[ISSEI] The president
and her mom have been acting
hella weird lately.
Not just them,
but everyone.
Like they're expecting
something from me.
It's either one of two things.
The first is that I've somehow
hurt the prez's feelings
without realizing it because
I'm a total dick nugget,
or it could be something else.
And if that's the case, then...
[ISSEI] There are three guys
in the Gremory household.
The prez has always cared
about her family,
but something's off.
Like, she obviously treats
me differently
than the other dude‐bros
in her service.
For starters, she really digs
the romance stuff
or whatever with me.
I mean, I don't think
girls typically offer
to ride you harder
than a carousel horse
if their feelings are just
indifferent, do they?
No, that only happens in porn...
and maybe
those harem animes.
So taking her recent actions
into consideration...
Could the president
have feelings for me?
Like for real?
There's no way.
She's the master of our house,
and I'm just her servant!
We're both devils, sure,
but at the very most
I'm only a pawn to her!
Literally!
But... what if she does love me?
And I'm in love with her, too.
Not just because
she's my master,
but also because I love her
as a woman.
After all this time, I've seen
so many sides of her.
Her brilliance. Her nobility.
Her beauty.
Her kindness.
Her bangin' bod.
Her stubborn temper.
Sometimes she's mature.
Sometimes childish.
'Cause of all that, I started
to crush on her pretty hardcore.
She really is the ideal woman.
I'd love to kick things up
a notch and actually date her,
but is that even possible?
I wanna tell her how I feel,
but I'm scared.
I guess the real question is,
does the prez
actually like me back?
What if I ask and I'm wrong?
It'll ruin everything.
I don't want things
to change.
Damn, so what do I do?
This blows. Why do women have
to be so complicated?
[AKENO laughs]
You don't know how you feel,
and you're calling
us complicated?
[gasps]
[yelps, screams]
Oh! Ouch, my pride.
Uh, did you hear me?
‐Obvi.
‐[nervous chuckle]
Yeah, well.
Looks like I suck at thinking
about the president's
feelings, huh?
[ANEKO]
Yes, you've sucked very hard.
But to be honest,
you haven't been thinking
about the feelings of any women
in the Gremory family,
including Asia,
Koneko and myself.
[sighs]
Then again...
we're just as guilty because
we haven't been trying
to understand what
you're going through.
Uh, what I'm going through?
Now it's your turn.
Uh. Uh, see ya later, jacket.
Here's the thing.
See, I know Rias
is very important to you,
but if you're ever going to be
able to understand her
and what she needs,
you'll need to be healed first.
[chuckles]
We're going to suck out the
power of your dragon right here.
[yelps]
Don't just stare,
hold me already.
Huh? Uh...
I said hold me, Brainiac.
I'm going to perform healing
sage arts like I've done before.
[ISSEI]
Oh! If you feel anything move,
‐it's a compliment!
‐[KONEKO] Okay. Here goes.
[ISSEI moans]
You're gonna suck my finger off.
[gasps]
[energy humming]
[giggles]
I shall heal you as well.
Okay.
[Aneko sighs, giggles]
Sometimes, you seem scared
when you look at us,
and we could never
quite figure out why,
but now we finally understand.
Yes, except only the people who
were actually there that day
would be able to put
two and two together.
Please tell us
the truth, Issei.
You're still hurting over
Raynare's betrayal, aren't you?
‐[gasps]
‐Would you die for me?
[laughs]
Don't worry. That date was
everything I could want.
I was so bored,
I couldn't wait to kill you.
I love a man who takes control!
Where was this
when we were dating, huh?
[grunts]
Please, Issei, I need your help.
You'd never actually let those
devils hurt me, would you?
And I love you.
So won't you help me
defeat these scary devils?
If we do that, then you
and I can be together forever.
She was
my very first girlfriend,
and she just killed me,
and she killed Asia.
She lied to me,
she used me,
And in the end I‐‐
I truly hated that bitch, and...
[sobbing]
I'm actually afraid
of something like that
happening again.
[crying]
It's hard,
'cause I love gozangas,
but they remind me of her!
‐[crying]
‐It's okay, Issei,
because I love you so much.
I want to be
with you forever.
[ISSEI]
Asia.
I admire you,
and yearn for you.
You're the most
dependable guy that I know.
I truly mean it when I say
I want to be with you forever.
I can't imagine life
without you in it.
I wouldn't worry too much
about Rias, because I think
it'd be impossible
for her to really hate you.
After all, you always fight
harder and more passionately
for her than anyone else.
All of us in the Gremory family
are able to see that.
Regardless of what
the future may hold,
I really do believe
you can overcome this.
You're a strong person,
you just have to believe
in yourself a little more.
[crying]
‐[chuckles]
‐[gasps]
Exactly. Don't forget how many
of us love you, Issei.
Ditto. It's past time
to put the memory
of that fallen angel slut
into the "Fuck it" bucket.
‐Such a lady.
‐Koneko's right, though.
So, from now on,
the only Fallen Angel
you need haunting
your memories is me.
We've got your back,
so try to be more confident.
Hard to argue with that logic.
The point is, we all want
to be closer to you
and lend our support
as much as we can.
You do?
Of course, silly.
That includes Rias, Xenovia,
Irina, Rossweisse, Kiba, Gasper,
and everyone else
in the Gremory family.
We all love you so much,
and we want you
to succeed and be happy.
I wish you could see
the wonderful things we see
when we look at you.
You'll just have to trust us.
[chuckles]
You're right, yeah.
You guys have
always been there for me.
And... I promise
to return the favor.
Let's stay together...
for the rest of our lives!
That way I can love you forever.
Please!
That sounds good to me.
I want to love you forever,
too, Issei.
Oh my. This is a real pickle,
since I also want
‐to love you forever.
‐Speaking of pickles,
I'd like to claim the one
I'm currently sitting on.
[gasps]
‐[door opens]
‐Uhh...
[XENOVIA]
Hey, Irina! Check this out!
‐Huh?
‐They're in here, chowing down
on Issei's man ham without us!
Yo! We want in on that action,
‐so make some room!
‐[gasps]
I've got dibs on the pork juice.
Uh, I dunno what I should do!
But I have to think
about Lord Michael,
and doing this would be
a big win for heaven!
[clears throat]
Okay, I'm going in,
so save me some
of that ham bone, Xenovia!
Whoa‐ho‐ho!
That's my lead singer
and his back‐up vocalists
you're talking about,
and they are not meant
for consumption!
That's right, and I have
front row seats to the show!
Don't be greedy!
Concerts are a group event!
Okay then,
I've got dibs on the encore!
Yay sloppy seconds!
[ANEKO] That's fine.
The real party is
always backstage, anyway.
Right, Koneko?
I'd rather it be
a purr‐ivate party. Meow!
[yelps, thuds]
[laughter]
[ISSEI]
It's weird, sometimes I feel
like I'll never understand
what chicks are thinking,
but I'm so grateful.
Asia, Akeno,
Koneko,
Xenovia, Irina,
thanks for telling me
what I needed to hear.
I'll try to see me
the way all of you do.
Maybe then
I can give the president
the answer she's looking for.
Maybe then I can finally
tell her how I really feel.
[ISSEI] Whoa.
This place is legit as fuck!
[AZAZEL] Yep, this is what
the floating city of Agares
looks like up close.
Originally, the Bael faction
wanted to have
the game in their domain,
but then
Archduke Agares intervened
between the Great Satan
and the Great King.
Blah, blah, blah, so the game is
being held here. We know.
Hold on, I just thought
of something.
is our rating game supposed
to represent the battle
between the Great King Bael
and Great Satan Lucifer?
Well. There are some people
who would look at it that way,
‐so I guess, yeah.
‐Talk about reading into it.
Meanwhile, we're only
doing the rating game
because we wanna
kick some ass.
[laughs] Then that's all
that really matters.
I think it's a good idea
to just focus on the match.
Even if you lose,
none of it will affect
Sir Zech's political standing,
although it would
probably make the politicians
backing the Great King
and Sairaorg pretty happy,
but try not to worry
about that.
[ISSEI] I guess
I shouldn't be surprised
about how much
politics come into play.
[AZAZEL]
True.
♪
[cameras clicking]
What took you guys so long?
The match isn't scheduled
to begin until nightfall,
so until then,
they've asked you to wait
in your designated room
next to the venue.
[GROUP]
Hmm?
[AZAZEL] Well, if it isn't
the god who rules over the dead
of the Netherworld.
Hello, Sir Hades.
What brings such
an avid devil and angel hater
such as yourself here?
[laughs]
I can't help it.
You crows have been squawking
so incessantly,
I had to see what
all the noise was about.
It's nice to see
the Welsh Dragon.
‐[breathes shakily]
‐I will admit that I miss
watching you and
the Vanishing Dragon run wild
in the depths of hell.
It gets rather dull without you.
At least tonight's match
should be entertaining.
Do me favor and try not to die.
I don't want to have
to reap your souls.
Putting the crazy Skeletor
doppelganger aside,
I'm actually kinda surprised
that Lord Zeus
and Lord Poseidon
are gonna be there.
I'm not. That's how much
attention this game is getting.
‐[door opens]
‐[RISER] Excuse me.
Hello. I'm here for the match.
‐Huh.
‐[gasps]
‐Whoa! Riser?
Big brother?
You must be excited.
Your match today is garnering
the same attention
as a professional one.
Hopefully you'll be able
to show off your strength here.
It would certainly make
a strong point.
I'm more nervous than excited,
since I'm not as talented
as Sona in battle tactics,
nor am I as powerful
as Lord Sairaorg.
All I have is
a wonderful family.
Battle tactics and strength
are all well and good,
but they're both something
that anyone can gain
with enough experience
and effort.
And more importantly,
someone who has
a natural talent
for finding and gathering
skilled individuals
is special.
I honestly believe
it's that particular ability
which has given you
the wonderful family
you're so quick
to boast about, Rias.
Perhaps, but they could also
be here just because of Issei.
You're the one who recruited
the Red Dragon Emperor,
so it's still because of you.
Take a look around.
[footsteps]
See? These people
are here to support you,
because you all
share something.
Believe in their strength.
[gasps]
Hmm. I should go.
‐Oh, and Red Dragon.
‐Huh?
[RISER] I've never
forgotten the way it felt
when you punched me
during our game.
Know that I intend
to return the favor.
But I can't do that
until you win this match
and come up
to the professional league.
Right! Don't you worry.
Next time we battle, I'm gonna
wipe the floor with you.
Also, you'd better
watch over my little sister.
If you make her cry,
I will roast you alive
and serve you for dinner.
Eyes on the mini babe.
‐You got it!
‐Uh, excuse me!
He's not my keeper!
[ALL laugh]
Oh, that's right.
I'm supposed to give you
a message from Sir Zechs.
He said he needed
a moment of your time.
Huh?
Thank you for coming.
Your fans sent you
a little something
that I wanted you to see.
Really? They did?
So what is it?
Go on and take
a look for yourself.
I hope you win the game,
Grabbin' Dragon,
and good luck out there!
‐[KIDS] We love you!
‐[chuckles]
‐Mr. Grabbin' Dragon...
‐Kapow!
‐...you're the coolest!
‐Take that!
‐Summon Tig Ol' Bitties! Yay!
‐Boop, boop, go!
‐[laughs]
‐Balance break! Yeah!
Do your best, today!
I'll be cheering you on as loud
as I can from home, okay?
I hope you win! [laughs]
This is what
I wanted to show you.
Children from all
over the Underworld
will be watching tonight.
They admire you, Issei.
No matter what,
there will always be
adult politics in these games.
That's how matches
have always been.
Even so, I'd like to be
so bold as to ask you a favor.
If at all possible,
can you please fight
for the dreams
of these children?
And while it's important
to protect their dreams,
I hope you'll fight just
as hard to protect your own.
Yeah, of course I will.
Because after all,
I am the Grabbin' Dragon!
[CROWD cheering, applauding]
I'm too nervous
to go out there.
Don't freak. If you do,
just imagine the audience
buck naked or whatevs.
Hey, Xenovia, is it true
that Irina is leading
‐a cheer squad for us?
‐Totally.
I think she's set up a small
group over in the fan section
of the special
Grabbin' Dragon seating area.
[NAUD]
Coming in from the East Gate,
may I present
the Sairaorg Bael team!
[CROWD cheering]
And coming in
from the West Gate,
may I present
the Rias Gremory team!
Before we go out there,
I just want to thank
each and everyone of you
for being a part
of my precious family.
Is everyone ready?
Let's show them
what we're made of!
[ALL]
Right!
[CROWD cheering]
[NAUD] How is everybody
doing this fine evening?
I'm Naud Gamigin,
your emcee for tonight!
I'd like to take a moment
to present the arbiter
for the game.
Give it up
for Rudiger Rosenkreutz!
We also have
a few special guests.
Welcome one
of our commentators,
you know him
as the Governor‐General
of the Fallen Angels.
It's Azazel!
‐[gasps]
‐Achtung, darlings!
We also have with us
the current champion
of the Rating Game. It's...
Diehauser Belial!
[CROWD cheering]
Let's discuss the rules,
shall we?
Tonight we'll be utilizing
a popular variant item.
Behold,
a Dice Figure Game!
At this time I'd like to invite
the Kings from each team
to step up to the special
platform, please.
For those not familiar
with the dice game,
I will take this moment
to go over the rules
of how this will work.
For each round, the Kings
will use a normal six‐sided die.
Both Kings will then roll
their individual die
and the resulting total
of both numbers
will decide the members
of the match.
For example, if the numbers
rolled are equal to eight,
each team may
send out members
that add up
to that specific number.
The value
of each player depends
on what sort of evil piece
they consist of.
Pawns are one point,
knights and bishops
are three points,
rooks are five points,
and queens are equal
to nine points.
Multiple players may
be chosen for the match,
so in the case
of eight points,
the King may send out
two knights to participate,
or it's also
considered acceptable
to mix and match
your evil pieces,
so you could also send out
a three‐point knight
and a five‐point rook to fight.
The number of evil pieces
used for a family member
is also taken into account
for calculating
who to send into battle.
For instance,
Issei Hyodo is made up
of eight pawn pieces,
so he has a point value
equal to the number eight.
But remember,
ladies and gentlemen,
you cannot send out
the same piece consecutively,
so choose carefully.
And of course,
let's not forget
about the Kings of each family.
Like normal, the game will end
if the King is defeated,
and so, after taking
all of the above factors
into consideration,
the review board has decided
what the point value will be
for each the two Kings.
All right, my dears,
hold onto your hats,
because we are about to
announce those numbers!
Sairaorg Bael
will be worth 12 points!
Rias Gremory
will be worth eight points!
Now, now, Lord Sairaorg may
have a higher point value,
but that also means
he cannot participate in a match
without a maximum
roll of 12,
so that could work
to Rias Gremory's advantage!
The last rule is regarding
Phoenix Tears!
Thanks to the Phoenix family,
each team will have
one vial available to use
at any time during the game.
Great, meaning we have
to prepare for the possibility
of defeating Sairaorg
not once, but twice.
Balls.
[NAUD]
Enough, my blood‐thirsty rubes!
‐Let's get started!
‐The match begins now.
Lord Sairaorg Bael
and Princess Rias Gremory,
let's get ready to rumble!
[cheering]
[RUDIGER] It's time
to decide the first match.
Kings, please pick up your die!
Let's roll!
[NAUD]
Sairaorg Bael has rolled a one!
Rias Gremory has rolled a two!
The total is three.
Since the value of the pawns
on each side is too high,
only a bishop or a knight
may be chosen
to participate
in the first round.
Now the question is whom
will each family choose
to send out
for this opening match?
[RUDIGER]
You have five minutes to plan.
Please choose your champion
within that time frame.
[IRINA] This is it. I wonder
who they'll choose to go first?
[RUDIGER] The five‐minute
time limit is nearly up.
Kiba! It's all up to you,
so go kick some "A."
I'm planning on it.
‐[chuckles]
‐[humphs]
[NAUD] It looks like
the participants from each team
are now entering
the designated battle field.
The Gremory family has chosen
the Noble of God‐like Speed,
the Knight of Princess Rias.
Give it up for Kiba Yuto!
[CROWD cheering]
Finally, the game's
about to begin.
♪
[ISSEI] "As a family member
of Rias Gremory."