[ISSEI]
What's up?
I'm Issei Hyodo!
My dream is to become
the Harem King.
But you should know...
most people
wouldn't refer to me
as a normal
high school sophomore.
That's cause I'm, like,
totally a devil!
Seriously! I'm not lying!
I sorta died,
but then, a sexy devil
brought me back to life.
Her name is Rias Gremory,
and she's hot AF!
She made me the pawn in her
chessboard devil family thing,
and I've been hangin'
with her crew ever since.
Oh yeah, and the legendary
Red Dragon Emperor
dwells within me. NBD.
One day, we were just about
to get our sports festival on
and this creeper showed up
thinkin' he was gonna
marry Asia.
Diodora Astaroth, AKA
upper‐class devil dickhead.
I mean, so what if he comes
from a good family
and has abs that won't quit.
That guy's a bag
of dirty douche water.
I was like, "Screw him!
"I'm never gonna
let anyone force Asia
to do anything
she doesn't want to do!"
I got super pissed
and then I super kicked
that twatsicle's ass.
Asia was saved,
and all was awesome.
[heroic music playing]
[ASIA]
Thank you, Issei.
[ISSEI]
It's time for us to go home.
[ASIA]
All right!
But first, I'd like
to say a little prayer.
[ISSEI] You just got rescued,
what's there to pray about?
[ASIA]
That's a secret!
[energy charges]
[ALL gasping]
[energy whooshes]
[ALL grunting]
Asia?
♪ ♪
[energy whooshes]
[RIAS]
Who are you?
[SHALBA] Dear little sister
of the despicable
and fake "Devil King."
Most know me
as Shalba Beelzebub.
However, who I am
is the one and only
true descendant of
the Great Devil Beelzebub.
Beelzebub's what?
[DIODORA]
Please, Shalba. Help me.
Just imagine it.
Both the old
and current devil kings
combining their strength.
‐[energy bolt rings]
‐Why, Shalba?
[screaming]
You were a fool.
How dare you
align yourself with me.
Sister of the impostor,
Sir Zechs.
Please don't
take this personally,
but I believe I shall
have you die here, as well.
Of course.
You were behind the death
of the
Glasya‐Labolas heir, too.
But why bother involving Asia
in your murderous plan?
You'll suffer for
what you did to her!
[ISSEi whispers]
Asia.
Asia?
Where did you run off to?
Come on.
Let's go home.
Issei.
[ISSEI crying]
Please, Asia.
We were gonna win the race
in the school sports festival.
We...
We still need to practice.
[wailing]
[RIAS]
Issei!
[ISSEI]
Rias?
Do you know where
Asia might've gone?
We need to find her fast,
so we can leave.
Help me.
We can't leave without her.
She's practically family.
Oh, Issei.
Now, who would have thought
the princess of
the Gremory household
had such horrible taste.
Would the red filth
like to know
where that girl went?
I sent her far beyond
our reality.
Into the Dimensional Gap.
The exposure has surely
consumed her flesh.
To put it simply,
the bitch is dead.
[ISSEI gasps]
[ISSEI sobs]
[energy charging]
[DDRAIG]
As for you, devil,
the one who calls
himself "Shalba."
[gasps]
[DDRAIG]
You made a poor decision,
and now you must pay!
[energy whooshing]
[ALL gasping]
Issei!
[shouts]
‐I, who shall awaken.
‐[SPIRIT BOY] It's starting.
[SPIRIT GIRL]
The time has finally come.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
I am the Heavenly Dragon
who stole the principle
of domination for God.
[SPIRIT WOMAN]
It has always been this way.
[SPIRIT MAN]
That is correct.
Always and forever.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
I mock the infinite,
and fret over the dream.
[SPIRIT MAN]
What the world desires.
[SPIRIT WOMAN]
What the world rejects.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
I shall become
the Red Dragon
of Domination.
[SPIRIT MAN]
Has always been power.
[SPIRIT WOMAN]
Has always been love.
[ISSEI and SPIRITS]
I shall drown you
in the depths of
crimson purgatory.
What is that?
What is that?!
His aura and power
are incredible to behold!
And dangerous.
[roaring]
Asia!
[DDRAIG]
Juggernaut Drive!
[explosion]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT roars]
Oh, Issei.
[roaring continues]
[gasps]
[screaming]
[SHALBA]
You monster!
[grunting]
[energy charging]
[screams]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT roars]
[energy surging]
[DDRAIG echoing]
Divide!
[roars]
[SHALBA]
He's using Vali's power?
Why must Vali always insist
on standing in my way?
[explosion]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT growling]
It's too much.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT
roars in distance]
[roaring continues]
[deep rumbling]
[roaring]
[panting]
President!
Rias, please.
That isn't Issei anymore.
[roaring continues]
[snarling]
♪ ♪
[SHALBA]
No! You bastard!
This creature must be
the Dragon of Domination!
I have no intention of dying
in a place like this.
Not by your hand!
[energy charging]
[energy surges]
I can't move.
My legs!
Gasper, you can't stop time
right now, can you?
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT growls]
[DDRAIG echoing]
Boost!
We can't stay here, Rias!
If we do, we'll die.
Come on. I think
we should retreat!
I won't.
Please, Rias!
[KIBA]
I'm sorry. We're going!
[DDRAIG echoing, continues]
Boost!
You can't!
Don't you realize
I am the descendant
of a true devil king?
You're a mere dragon!
[DDRAIG]
Longinus Smasher!
Don't you dare!
Red Dragon and White Dragon,
damn you both!
[explosion]
[rumbling]
Where's Issei?
[energy surges]
[ALL gasping]
[roars]
[intense music playing]
[roaring continues]
Issei.
What's wrong?
He took out Shalba,
but he's not reverting
back to himself.
[VALI]
Ah, the Juggernaut Drive.
[RIAS]
Vali!
Interesting find.
I sensed a change
in Issei's power,
and came to see why.
Also...
[gasps]
Asia!
♪ ♪
[BIKOU] This little healer
is one of yours,
is she not?
We just happened
to cross paths with her
while we were moving
through the Dimensional Gap.
This is one very lucky girl.
Don't worry. She's alive.
Asia!
Oh, Asia!
[XENOVIA crying]
[VALI]
Unfortunately...
it looks like your servant had
an incomplete transformation.
Issei, no.
Do you know if there's
any way to change him back?
There's a chance.
It might happen naturally,
but if not, he'll use up
his life force,
and that will kill him.
[RIAS] What if we tell him
Asia's all right?
‐Asia! Asia!
‐[VALI] Pointless.
He can't hear you.
If you merely approach him,
you'll die.
[gasps]
But far be it from me
to stop you.
What about the power
of the White Dragon Emperor?
Please, Vali!
Do you think you're
strong enough?
I'm begging you to do
whatever it takes to save Issei!
Help us!
Anything, everything.
No matter the cost,
we will do it!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT
roaring in distance]
The only thing
I think might work
is to find a way to get
deep into his psyche
and then shake things up a bit.
Into his psyche, huh?
[KONEKO]
Shake things up.
[ALL gasping]
[gasps]
Bingo bongos.
[BIKOU] All you need to do
is show him some boobs.
[VALI sighs]
We can't show him anything
until he's out of that state.
[RIAS] Then how do we
get him out of it?
[VALI] It's been said
since ancient times
that music has been known
to calm the anger of a dragon.
I'm not aware what
the right songs are, though.
‐[KIBA] Music?
‐[XENOVIA] Music?
‐[KONEKO] Music?
‐[AKENO] Music?
Music?
Music!
[IRINA shouting]
I know the right song!
[gasps] Huh?
[KIBA]
No way!
[RIAS]
Irina Shido?
Why are you here?
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT roars]
Goodness gracious!
This is worse than I expected!
[AKENO]
We know.
What are you doing here?
You know the bigwigs
like to keep up to date
on what's going on with you.
Well, things looked bad.
So Devil King Lucifer
and Azazel sent me.
I've brought you this:
the ultimate secret weapon!
Check it out!
Can you believe
Lord Odin was able to
transport something that big?
The God of the North
is amazing!
Oh, and that beard!
Talk about a work of art!
Everybody, get ready!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT snarls]
Here we go! Play!
[low whirring]
[growling]
[ISSEI on video]
Did someone say boobies?
[RIAS]
Huh?
[ISSEI on video]
Breast Dragon Emperor!
[CHILDREN]
It's grabbin' time!
[CHILDREN cheering and laughing]
[upbeat music playing]
[singing in Japanese]
[singing continues]
What is this nightmare?
‐[CHILDREN laughing]
‐[singing continues]
[CHILDREN]
Pinch 'em!
Yay!
[KIBA] Yeah,
so Issei was summoned
to the TV studio
not too long ago.
From what I understand,
he recorded this song
for a children's show.
Don't blame just him.
Guess who wrote
the music and lyrics.
They actually made time
to do this.
It's awful and I love it.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT snorting]
[RIAS]
He's reacting!
[KONEKO]
Anyone else completely shocked?
[AKENO] Irina, please
don't stop playing the song.
[IRINA]
Yes, ma'am! I'm on it!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Boobies.
[VALI]
I, who shall awaken,
am the Heavenly Dragon
who has lost all
to the principle of domination.
I envy the infinite
and yearn for the dream.
I shall become the
White Dragon of Domination.
Albion.
[ALBION]
Vanishing Dragon.
Balance Breaker!
[music and singing continues]
[ALBION echoing]
Divide!
[roars]
[singing continues]
Go to Issei, Rias.
He needs you now.
You and your massive bosom.
What I'm saying is you have
to let him grab your tits!
Hey!
When he did it before,
he achieved Balance Breaker.
Your boobs gave him strength.
They should have the
opposite effect too, right?
Letting him fondle you
may be the only way
to save him!
You think?
[AKENO]
Your girls can do it, Rias.
I know they can!
[AKENO chuckles]
I get how you feel.
It's just not fair,
but no one else
has what you have.
[singing continues]
[BIKOU laughing]
This is stupid.
[KONEKO]
Sure is.
Yeah! All we can do is laugh.
Issei's... you know.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT straining]
I want to poke them.
[exhales deeply]
For Issei!
[singing continues]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Funbags.
[singing continues]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Breasticles.
[breathing heavily]
[singing continues]
Fine, if this is what it takes
to bring my Issei back.
[gasps]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT shudders]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT
breathing heavily]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Jubblies.
[laughing lecherously]
[RIAS groans]
[energy surging]
[singing continues]
Well, imagine that.
Issei Hyodo's limit switch
just happens to be
Rias Gremory's rack.
This is my favorite thing today!
[chuckles]
Oh, Issei. Go figure.
You really are
the Grabbin' Dragon.
[gentle music playing]
Rias?
I'm here, Issei.
I'm right here.
[ISSEI gasps]
Asia.
Asia!
I'm okay, Issei.
You sure you're all right?
‐I'm so‐‐
‐Oh, Asia!
We're supposed to be
friends forever and ever.
That's the deal!
So don't ever leave me
like that again!
‐Promise!
‐[ASIA] I won't.
At least, I'll try not to.
I think that I can
promise you that much.
Hey, man, I'm sorry if
I caused you any trouble.
Nah. I don't mind it
every so often.
‐It was worth it.
‐[energy crackling]
[ALL gasp]
[VALI]
Issei Hyodo, take a look.
This is what I came
out here to see.
What is it?
[VALI]
The Apocalypse Dragon.
Written in the Revelation.
Great Red.
He is considered the true
Red Dragon God Emperor.
One day, I'll be the true
White Dragon God Emperor.
But to do that, I must
take out the Dragon of Dragon.
So that's it.
That's your dream.
[ORPHIS]
Great Red.
‐It's been a while.
‐[ISSEI gasps]
That's just tape!
Meet Orphis, Ouroboros Dragon.
Also known as the
Leader of the Chaos Brigade.
[ISSEI]
That's‐‐ seriously?
Oh, yes, Red.
Soon, I'll finally
obtain my silence.
[AZAZEL]
Hey, Issei!
You seem to be back to normal.
[ISSEI]
Azazel, old man!
[AZAZEL] I knew that song
would bring you back to us.
It sure doesn't take
a lot to figure you out.
You're welcome for those
amazing lyrics, by the way.
[ISSEI] Eh, seemed kinda
repetitive to me.
[GROUP laughing]
[AZAZEL]
Blame Sir Zechs, then.
It was all his idea anyway.
[VALI]
Tell me something, Issei.
Do you want to defeat me?
[ISSEI]
Hmm?
I mean, yeah!
But it's not like you're
the only one I wanna beat.
There's still Kiba,
and Saji, too.
There's, like, a ton of you!
Hmph!
I feel the same.
I also find it
rather strange
that both of us would have
so many goals and dreams
that take such priority over
our eventual fated battle.
We must be unusual vessels
for the dragons
this time around.
You're probably right!
That said. Someday...
Yeah! Someday,
your ass is grass.
C'mon, I can't
allow you to divide
Rias and Akeno's precious
pairs in half, can I?
Get strong, Issei.
Don't you dare
let me down. [chuckles]
We're off.
Bye, Grabbin' Dragon!
You too, Switch Princess!
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I swore that I would
protect you, no matter what.
[laughs softly]
Asia.
Let's go back for real.
You wanna go home, right?
I do!
[groaning]
[ALL gasping, clamoring]
[delicate piano playing]
Shalba has now fallen,
and Vali will hardly
make it to the top.
What are your thoughts?
Should the Hero Faction
make a move soon?
No.
[SIEGFRIED]
You do realize
we will have to make
a move at some point.
The all‐powerful
Sacred Gear within you
will not be patient
much longer.
[CAO CAO]
The True Longingus.
Will this spear lead me
to domination...
or something else?
[fireworks booming]
[CROWD cheering and applauding]
[ANNOUNCER] Our next event
is the three‐legged race.
All competitors
to the start line!
All runners, gather up!
[ISSEI shouting]
Asia!
[panting]
Issei, you came!
I'm so happy!
[ISSEI]
I may not be back to 100% yet,
but I'm still gonna keep
the promises I made!
[ASIA crying]
[ISSEI]
What'd I say?
Why are you crying?
[ASIA]
It's okay!
I'm just glad you're here!
[ATTENDANT]
Next in line, please be ready.
[ISSEI] All right!
Ready to win first place?
[ASIA]
Yeah!
[starting gun fires]
[ISSEI] Asia, I want you
to stay with me forever!
Please don't leave me again.
[ASIA]
I won't!
[CROWD]
Go Issei and Asia!
You can do it!
[indistinct cheering]
[ISSEI]
We did it, Asia!
We got first place!
I can't believe it!
‐That was amazing!
‐Yep!
We really did it, Issei.
‐[ISSEI moans]
‐[ASIA gasps]
Asia, I want you
to go heal him
with your Sacred Gear, please.
You won't be seen behind
the gym, so take him there.
Okay!
Come this way,
and you can lean on me
if you want to.
I'm sorry.
Go on. You can do this.
[energy pulsing]
That was awesome, thanks!
I feel like normal again.
I'll probably be able to win
the rest of the events now.
[ASIA] Issei, I've wanted
to tell you something,
but you've been
sleeping constantly.
♪ ♪
[ISSEI moaning]
Uh, whoa.
That's nice.
I wanted to say
I love you, Issei.
And I‐‐
I'll stay by you forever.
[gasps]
Are you okay?!
[goofy laughter]
[sighs]
[ASIA]
It's true, though.
I'll never stop
loving you, Issei.
[ISSEI] That's right!
Let's go to Kyoto!