[ISSEI grunting]
Take this!
[SHADOW]
Foxfire? Ha!
That pathetic little flame
can't hurt me.
[DDRAIG]
What's your plan?
[ISSEI] Kick his ass,
of course. Do it!
[DDRAIG] Boost! Boost! Boost!
Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost!
[DDRAIG]
Transfer!
[SHADOW grunts]
[ISSEI] You want the heat?
You can't handle the heat!
Is that Dragon's Fire?
[SHADOW] Damn it!
Fuck you, Red Dragon Emperor!
[ISSEI] Listen.
You'll die if we continue.
[SHADOW grunts]
If it's for him,
it would be my honor!
[ISSEI]
You'd really be okay with dying
for that twat‐cicle, Cao Cao?
[SHADOW]
You know how it is.
Possessors of a sacred gear
are treated like dogs
and persecuted
everywhere we go!
It doesn't matter
what we do,
we're still just the shit
on the bottom
of everyone else's shoes.
But Cao Cao was able to destroy
those half‐baked
misconceptions
and change
my life for the better!
Everything was total crap
before I met him,
so I don't care if I die!
[ISSEI] That bitch‐ass punk
is just using you.
[SHADOW]
So what if he is?
Get down off
your stupid moral high horse!
Thanks to him,
my shit‐tastic life
finally has a purpose!
My powers are important!
They'll help Cao Cao destroy
devils, angels, and gods!
What could be
more amazing than that?
Enough talk. Die, devil!
[ISSEI]
Damn straight I'm a devil!
But in the end,
there's still people
depending on me
to protect this city.
That's why I have no choice
but to take each
and every one of you down.
You've got some moves.
[ISSEI]
Thanks. Let's go save your mom.
[KUNOU] Mmm.
[ISSEI]
Hey! Sorry it took so long!
‐[KIBA] No worries.
‐[ISSEI] You guys okay?
‐[ASIA and IRINA] Yes!
‐[XENOVIA] Why wouldn't we be?
[ROSSWEISSE groans]
[ALL chuckle]
Oh, what's up
with the new sword?
It just arrived from the church
a few moments ago.
It's the modified Durandal.
[ISSEI] Mmm. Nothing turns
me on like perfect timing.
[ALL]
Huh?
I guess it'd be rude
to keep them waiting.
Uh‐huh.
[CAO CAO] Ah, look who
finally made it to the party.
Where's the babe?
‐[rustling]
‐[gasps]
[KUNOU gasps]
Mother!
It's Kunou! I've come for you!
What's wrong? Say something!
Don't you recognize me?
You bastards!
What did you do to my mother?
Oh, did you forget?
I was sure I told you earlier
that she's helping us out
with a little experiment.
Here, see for yourself.
‐[clangs]
‐[groaning]
[GROUP gasps]
[howls]
I know that's your mom and all,
but for fox sake.
Mother.
[CAO CAO]
A nine‐tailed fox is
the absolute
highest class of youkai.
The city of Kyoto has
an unbreakable bond with them,
and as such,
it was built to ensure
that there's always
an ample supply of chi.
If we combine the power of
the youkai and Kyoto together,
then we'll be able to lure
Great Red into this dimension.
But what for?
I mean, the dude just likes
to chill out
in the Dimensional Gap!
It's not like
he's hurting anyone!
[CAO CAO]
You're not wrong.
However,
to no fault of his own,
he's become a bit
of a nuisance to my boss.
She wants to return home,
but it appears he's in the way.
You're saying... Orphis?
All of this, just so you can
kill Great Red?
That's your big plan?
Congratulations, you should
be proud you figured that out.
But, aren't you the least bit
interested in him?
For example, have you ever
really thought about the effect
of the Dragon Eater against
the Red Dragon God Emperor?
My thoughts are reserved
for boob‐related matters only,
now hand over that fox MILF
or you'll have to answer to me!
That is enough, Issei.
The time for talk is over.
Now is the time for action.
Let's put an end
to this nonsense.
‐I'm ready whenever you are.
‐Yeah, me too.
Is it me or does
the Gremory family
have a thing
about dancing with death?
Well, ain't no party
like a dance party.
What's up, Vritra? Are you
ready to have a little fun?
I could be persuaded.
Which one's my prey?
That holy spear?
Or the fox youkai?
Either one works for me.
‐[clangs]
‐[gasps]
I'll go first.
It was nice knowing you!
[coughing]
Huh?
[shouts] Huh?
‐Whew!
‐Don't "whew" me!
You just gouged an asteroid‐
size hole with a friggin' sword!
As a guy, you should know
how important the first move is.
[whimpers]
Sure, rub it in.
This new Durandal
is something else.
The church used alchemy
to combine it with Excalibur.
As such, I gave her a new name.
It's Ex‐Durandal.
Of course, I thought they'd
be a little tougher to kill.
Well. I'm impressed!
Your group seems to be on par
with most of the other
high‐ranking devil families.
[chuckles]
It's rather surprising
that Shalba and Beelzebub
looked down on any of you.
Old men are like that, though,
always living in the past
instead of the present, right?
It's a shame, really.
Now then, your orders?
Yes, I suppose
we don't have all night.
Hey, Georg?
Start the experiment.
You got it.
From what I can make out,
he's using Norse magic,
demonic and fallen angel
spells, black and white magic,
maybe even fairy spells.
He must have an
extensive magic library!
[howls]
[GEORG]
The spell circle
and sacrificial placement
is optimal.
Now we just wait. The city's
power should attract Great Red.
Nice work.
I'll leave the rest up to you.
Okay, Siegfried,
go on, take your pick.
Who would you like to play with?
Hmm.
[gasps]
Next Jeanne, then Heracles.
Let's see. I'll pick that cute
little angel right there.
[IRINA gasps]
I've got dibs
on the silver‐haired lady.
[gags]
I'll take
the Red Dragon Emperor.
[chuckles]
Don't forget about Vritra.
Yo, Saji, do you think
you can handle the fox youkai?
See if you can maybe
get her to a safer spot.
All right. I'll take care
of the giant fox.
But hey, try not to die.
No promises, but yeah, you too.
Go, Vritra Promotion!
[roars]
Well, look at that.
One of the five
great dragon kings.
It's the Prison Dragon Vritra.
So he really has returned.
[ISSEI]
Asia! Take care of Kunou.
Right!
[ISSEI] Kunou,
can you take care of Asia?
Yes, of course! However...
[ISSEI]
Yeah, don't worry.
We're gonna do our best
to win this fight,
‐and save your mother!
‐Right!
[DDRAIG] Welsh Dragon,
Balance Breaker!
[ISSEI] Hey!
Are you stronger than Vali?
Who knows? But I will
tell you that I'm not weak,
even if I am
from the weak human race.
[ISSEI shouts]
[BOTH roar]
[AKENO] You know, Issei
hasn't contacted us in a while.
‐Aren't you worried?
‐[RIAS] No.
Though I guess
I feel a bit restless
since he's so far away,
but I'm sure everything's fine.
Totes. I'm sure the perv is
loving his last night in Kyoto.
Well, Kyoto can be
a city of temptations. Right?
Oh? Your lingerie.
You mean these? I just got them.
What do you think?
Well, they do hold boobs.
[AKENA giggles]
Wow, Rias.
You're certainly trying hard
to impress a boy
who's not even here.
You must really miss him.
Mmm. I do.
[ISSEI shouts]
[XENOVIA shouts]
[chuckles]
It looks like this is
a two‐sword job.
Let's spice things up, shall we?
I'll show both
of you a little trick.
My Balance Breaker!
[gasps]
He has six swords now?
These are the demon swords
Tyrfing and Dainsleif.
I also have a sword of light
that's perfect for devils.
[KIBA]
He's like an Asura.
And this is my Chaos Edge,
Asura Ravage.
Like my Twice Critical,
this Balance Breaker
is also a subspecies.
Show me what you've got!
Damn, girl, look at you go,
you're killin' it!
I gotta say,
you're pretty good for an angel!
[shouts]
This is Blade Blacksmith.
It's the holy version
of the demon thing
your cute friend's
using over there.
Better hold on tight now,
it gets better.
Check out my Balance Break.
[clinks, humming]
[roars]
No way, a dragon
made of holy swords?
[JEANNE]
You wanna know what I call him?
"Stake Victim" Dragon.
He's a subspecies, too.
Cool, huh?
Jeanne d'Arc, the holy maiden.
I can't believe I'm fighting
against her reincarnation.
But I have to do this for
Lord Michael and everyone else!
I can't let her win!
I guess we're
playing show n' tell.
Here's my Balance Break!
[shouting]
Pretty impressive stuff,
isn't it?
This is
Detonation Mighty Comet!
[shouts]
‐[beeps rapidly]
‐[gasps]
[gasps]
I'm sorry, my friends
can be real show offs.
They just love their toys.
[ISSEI] Ever heard
of overcompensation?
Might as well
whip yours out, too.
No thanks. Personally,
I think it's good for a man
to have at least a few secrets.
[chuckles]
Besides, I don't need
it to beat you.
That's enough chit‐chat.
Show me what you're capable of!
Come on.
[ISSEI growls]
Bring it!
[ISSEI grunts, gags]
Aw, it's not
that you're weak, per say.
You just have
a lot of openings.
[ISSEI breathes hard]
[gasps] Oh no!
[straining]
Holy crap. That was bad.
My, you were shockingly close
to dying just then.
It happens
so easily for you, huh?
I should probably remind you
that this particular weapon
is a Holy Spear,
and no matter how
strong you eventually become,
you'll never be able
to overcome its raw power,
because you are a devil.
[ISSEI pants]
[grunts]
[gasps]
Well, color me surprised.
I was sure that last part
would scare you off.
[ISSEI pants]
Of course I'm scared,
but I can't worry
about that shit right now.
Everyone's expecting me
to eff you up,
but if I can't even
get one punch in,
then I don't deserve to be
the Red Dragon Emperor.
[CAO CAO laughs]
How noble.
I think I get it.
You really are such
a fascinating individual.
I can see why Vali
likes you so much.
[ISSEI grunts]
[DDRAIG] Boost! Boost! Boost!
Boost! Boost! Boost!
Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost!
[ISSEI] I just have
to get my attack to connect!
[grunts]
Yeah, boy!
How's that for a counter?
Ascalon's power
should be more than enough
to knock you down
a peg or two. [gasps]
Phoenix tears?
Where'd you get those?
Well, it wasn't exactly legal.
[ISSEI]
What the hell?
[CAO CAO] Your aura
increased with your anger.
Be careful with that trick.
It's a weakness that may lead
to your ultimate undoing.
I mean, that's pretty much
how you triggered
your Juggernaut
Drive in the past, isn't it?
[ISSEI]
You can Juggernaut deez nuts!
[grunts, gasps]
[CAO CAO] Oh yeah, while you
were busy chopping off my arm,
I may have landed
some hits of my own.
Still, it was
a fairly decent attack.
I might have
to up my game.
[ISSEI grunts]
Hey, Ddraig.
Can you go ahead
and repair the armor?
[DDRAIG]
I'm already trying,
but the effects of the holy
spear are giving me
more trouble than I anticipated.
[JEANNE]
No fair, you're still fighting?
[ISSEI gasps]
Irina!
[SIEGRIED] Well, it is
the Red Dragon Emperor.
Of course he's stronger
than the others.
[ISSEI]
Kiba! Xenovia!
[HERACLES] I wish I'd gotten
to fight the Red Dragon Emperor.
[ISSEI gasps]
Rossweisse!
[CAO CAO] Listen, you're
very strong. You really are.
The sad truth of the matter is
you're just not strong
enough to defeat us.
Georg, can you give me
an update please?
[roaring]
[GEORG]
We're almost there.
I think Great Red should
be arriving any moment now.
[howls]
[CAO CAO] The fox youkai looks
like she's almost done for.
[chuckles]
[crying]
[AZAZEL]
Protect Kyoto and yourselves.
[ISSEI]
Azazel.
I'm sorry. I really
messed up this time.
‐[howling]
‐[KUNOU] Mother!
[ISSEI]
I promised I'd save her mom,
but I couldn't live up to that.
Why am I so useless?
Why can't I do anything
when it matters the most?
It was a nice try,
Red Dragon Emperor.
[ISSEI sobs]
No matter how badly I want it,
I'm just too damn weak
to beat him!
Is this my actual limit?
It's not... fair.
[sobs]
No, I don't wanna give up!
I wanna keep fighting,
but nothing I do seems to work.
[ELSHA]
Are you crying?
[gasps]
I know those boobs.
Yes, it's me.
Why are you crying?
Because... I'm a loser.
And I'm frustrated
that I can't do anything.
I'm a huge failure.
I just let everyone
I know down.
[ELSHA]
Yes, that is rather frustrating.
However, you're still you.
[AZAZEL]
Grabbin' Dragon!
Now there's a nickname for you.
You're different from Vali.
Forget about everyone else.
You should master the power
of the Red Dragon Emperor
in your own way.
[gasps, grumbles]
That's right.
I'm the Grabbin' Dragon.
Indeed. That is who you are.
The current Red Dragon Emperor.
The Grabbin' Dragon.
Embrace it,
and release the potential
that Belzard and I
saw within you.
The time has come at last.
Hold the orb up to the sky
and call it forth.
‐[ISSEI] Call what?
‐Well, the boobs
that are meant for you, Issei.
[GROUP gasps]
[ZOMBIES]
Boobies. Boobies.
[ISSEI]
Uh, what's happening?
[ELSHA] Hopping
from one person to the next,
that orb was able
to travel all over Kyoto.
The afterimages
of what it experienced
took on the form of people.
[ISSEI]
Whoa! So in a way,
there really is
a zombie perv‐ocalypse,
but with like shadow molesters!
‐[ZOMBIES] Bazongas.
‐[ISSEI] Wow.
There's a lot of 'em.
Well, this is odd,
and probably a first.
Is that an army
of zomboobies?
[ZOMBIES]
Boobies! Melon. Melon.
Boobies!
[ELSHA]
The preparations are complete!
Let's call it forth.
[ISSEI]
Uh, call what forth?
I already told you before.
Call for the boobs
that are meant
just for you, Issei.
[ISSEI]
Just... for me.
Yes, now do it!
[ISSEI]
Okay.
I summon...
[shouts]
summon...
Tig Ole Bitties!
Oh...!
[gasps]
[ISSEI] The school trip
is in pandemonium!