[AZAZEL grunts]
You can call me Cao Cao.
I'm a descendant of Cao Cao
of the Three Kingdoms.
Not to brag.
Are you the monsters
who kidnapped my mother?
Just what do you
intend to do with her?
If you must know,
we're planning
to use your mother
for a fun little experiment.
No, you can't! That's awful!
[CAO CAO] But first,
I want to give a proper hello
to Governor‐General Azazel
and the Red Dragon Emperor
and maybe exchange
a few blows.
[AZAZEL]
That's an odd greeting.
I'm more interested in
the fox yokai leader, though.
We have some business
we need to attend to,
so I'll have to ask
that you give her back.
[snickers]
You're more than welcome
to try and take her.
[ISSEI growls]
Leonardo, would you be a dear
and create some friends
for our guests to play with?
[grunts]
[energy charging]
Lovely,
the Annihilation Maker.
You have a good eye.
This Longinus is
capable of creating
any monster
the user desires,
including anti‐devil monsters.
[AZAZEL] To think a power that
could destroy the whole world
is in your faction's hands.
Unbelievable.
Well, hell.
This is total BS.
[DDRAIG]
Welsh Dragon.
Balance Breaker.
[AZAZEL]
Well, seeing as your boy
hasn't sent
titan‐class creatures
to each strategic point,
I assume the user
must still be an amateur.
You know what they say about
assuming things, don't you?
Though in this particular
instance, you'd be correct.
Luckily, he makes up
for that lack of skill
with another unique power.
‐[energy surging]
‐[explosion]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
An attack of light?
[CAO CAO]
Leonardo has the ability
to create special
anti‐monsters
that can target
any opponent's weakness,
which covers a lot
in your case.
[energy surging]
[XENOVIA]
We'll take these guys out first!
[grunts]
[KIBA]
Sounds like a plan to me!
[ISSEI]
Well this sucks monkey tits!
We're totally
outnumbered here!
What should we do?
How do we play this?
C'mon, think
for once in your life!
Wait a minute.
What would Rias do
if she were here?
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Kiba! Can you hear me?
[KIBA]
Yeah!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Use your power to make
some cool‐ass swords
that eat light,
then pass them out.
Okay!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Xenovia, guard Kunou and Asia!
Release your holy aura
and attack anyone
that tries to come close!
I'm on it!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
If things start to go south,
you can use this as a shield!
Right!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Irina, I need you
to hold the front lines
with Kiba!
Light's not a weakness for you,
since you're an angel, right?
Maybe not, but that doesn't mean
I can't take on damage.
Fine, whatever,
I'll do my best.
I am Lord Michael's ace
after all.
[grunting]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Perfect timing.
Asia! Promotion to bishop!
‐'Kay! Here!
‐[energy charging]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Eat this, biatch!
[AZAZEL] Cao Cao, why don't
we settle this man to man?
[AZAZEL‐JUGGERNAUT]
Let's go!
Of course,
it would be my pleasure.
[AZAZEL‐JUGGERNAUT]
I know why you really attacked
the leaders of each group.
It was to gather intel for
your anti‐monsters, wasn't it?
[CAO CAO]
It's so sweet of you to notice,
and thanks to your cooperation
we have all the data we need!
[AZAZEL‐JUGGERNAUT]
Don't thank me yet.
It's not like you can
create a monster
that's able to slay a god!
[CAO CAO] Why do that
when I can use my own hands?
[BOTH grunting]
[GIRLS]
Red Dragon Emperor!
We are taking you down!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Boo‐ya!
This is the perfect time to
try my titty‐talkin' technique.
Release Earthly desires!
Boobielingual!
[GIRLS]
Huh? What's happening?
[ISSEI]
Start talkin', Pillow Pals.
Tell me all of your
dirty little secrets!
[GIRL A'S BOOBS]
We're gonna totally confuse you
with some crazy moves,
and then slam you
with a chain attack!
[GIRL B'S BOOBS]
I'm going to hit you first,
from the right side.
[GIRL C'S BOOBS]
And I'll come at you head on.
[ISSEI]
So long boulder‐holders!
[GIRLS screaming]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Sorry, not sorry.
The Boobielingual
and Dress Breaker combo
is unstoppable!
[GIRLS screaming and crying]
How disgusting.
I don't think
I've ever witnessed
such an overly
lecherous attack before.
[ASIA chuckles nervously]
[SIEGFRIED]
Your reputation proceeds you.
No woman's breasts are safe
from the Grabbin' Dragon.
Your tricks won't work
on me though.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Like I'd want them to.
Ain't nobody wanna see
those hairy nips.
[SIEGFRIED laughs]
[SIEGFRIED] So, you are the
famous Gremory Family.
My name is Siegfried.
It's nice to meet you.
[XENOVIA] I knew I'd seen you
somewhere before.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Really?
[XENOVIA]
He's a known devil purger.
He used to be considered
a top‐class knight
by the churches.
Chaos Edge Sieg.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Oh, goodie.
Another exorcist
douche canoe.
While I'm flattered
that you know about me,
I believe introductions
have gone on long enough.
[KIBA grunting]
‐[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT] Kiba!
‐[XENOVIA shouts]
[XENOVIA grunting]
[grunts]
[XENOVIA shouts]
[KIBA panting]
No way! He has three arms?
Seriously? How?
[SIEGFRIED]
Demonic Emperor Sword Gram.
As the most powerful
demon sword,
it can take on any blade
without difficulty.
And then there's
Balmung and Notung,
which are also
legendary swords.
Last but not least,
this is Twice Critical,
the Dragon's Hand.
I assumed he might
have a Sacred Gear.
We need to be on our guard
until we know what
those weapons can do.
You think that's bad?
I haven't even activated
my Balance Breaker yet.
[rumbling]
[distant explosions]
[energy surge]
[rumbling]
[CAO CAO]
I guess the rumors
about the Gremory family
are true.
Especially you, Issei Hyodo.
I suppose it's no surprise
that your team's performance
is more optimal
with you around.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Whatchu talkin' about?
[CAO CAO]
Your naivety is charming.
See, even though your physical
and demonic power are pitiful,
your ability to gather people
and delegate tasks
is actually rather admirable.
Undoubtedly, it is that skill
which will likely make you
the most dangerous of
the Red Dragon Emperors.
[AZAZEL‐JUGGERNAUT]
Cao Cao.
What exactly does
the Hero Faction want?
[CAO CAO] Not that I'd expect
a fallen angel to understand,
but our mission is simple.
We merely want
to test our limits,
and see how far we can go
as humans.
[AZAZEL‐JUGGERNAUT]
But why?
[CAO CAO]
Think about it:
Devils, dragons, fallen angels,
and everything in between.
They have incredible power,
yet it's always humans
who ultimately defeat them.
It's embarrassing,
all things considered.
So I decided to undertake
this challenge,
and test my limits.
To see just how far I could go
as a human fighting
among the gods.
Surely you can understand that.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Maybe, if I spoke asshole.
‐[low rumbling]
‐[AZAZEL‐JUGGERNAUT] Hmm?
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Now what?
[MONSTER roaring]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Holy fuck nuggets!
[AZAZEL‐JUGGERNAUT]
Gogmagog?
A destructive weapon
created by the ancient gods.
They were supposed
to be decommissioned
and sealed away
in the Dimensional Gap.
So, how did one get up here?
Oh, hey. What's up?
The name is
Le Fay Pendragon.
I'm on Lord Vali's team.
Nice to meet ya!
He was like,
"Give them this message!"
So, here it goes.
[clears throat]
"I warned you
not to get in my way."
That's my Vali impression.
So now, you're in trouble!
[GOGMAGOG roars]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT exclaims]
[rumbling]
[giggles]
Hey.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT grunting]
I am, like, the biggest
Grabbin' Dragon fan.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Huh?!
So, can I...
please shake your hand?!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Uh, sure, I guess.
[squeals happily]
[GOGMAGOG grunting]
[GOGMAGOG groans]
[shattering]
Oh, no, he's hurting
my poor widdle Goggy Woggy!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Fuck me!
That was a mildly
annoying distraction.
Now, let's get back
to business, shall we?
I believe I was in the middle
of destroying your ass.
[snickering]
[ROSSWEISSE groans]
[ROSSWEISSE] Who the hell
is making all that noise?
[CAO CAO growls]
I'm tryin' to take
a friggin' nap over here!
But do you care? No!
Screw you!
[energy charging]
[energy surging]
[surging continues]
[AZAZEL‐JUGGERNAUT]
Oh, jeez.
There are too many
variables in this fight,
though I must admit
it's the perfect start
to our festival.
[moans]
[groans]
[AZAZEL‐JUGGERNAUT]
Oh!
[CAO CAO]
Governor‐General Azazel.
Tonight, we'll utilize
all that Kyoto has to offer
at the Nijo castle,
and who knows?
You may even find your coveted
nine‐tail fox leader there.
Either way, you're welcome
to join in the festivities.
[AZAZEL‐JUGGERNAUT]
The hell do you mean?
Come and find out.
[AZAZEL‐JUGGERNAUT]
Watch it!
The space we're in
is disappearing.
Everyone put away
your weapons!
[birds chirping]
[indistinct chatter]
[AZAZEL grunts]
Mother, please.
Hang in there.
[grunts]
[KIRYUU] Excuse me?
What is this crap?
That's a mean thing
to call yourself.
Gah, you know
what I meant, dumbass!
Why did you take such
awful pictures of me?
'Cause it's you!
Well, then why aren't
they more sexy?
[MATSUDA/ISSEI laughing]
[MOTOHAMA]
Don't worry!
I took some good ones, too.
Yeah? Damn, I look
fly as a mutha.
[MOTOHAMA]
Accidents do happen, I guess.
‐[MATSUDA] Oh, snap!
‐[IRINA] Hey! That's me!
[XENOVIA]
What a cutie pie!
[ASIA]
Soy cute. Oh, look!
[IRINA] That place had,
like, really good coffee.
[XENOVIA] Yeah,
I'm glad we stopped there.
[KIRYUU] Let's look
at the other pictures.
[ISSEI] No matter what,
we have to go home together.
Back to Kuoh Academy,
and back to Rias.
Here's the deal.
We've mobilized what firepower
we can around Nijo Castle.
Everyone else is organized
near Kyoto Station.
The Hero Faction hasn't
made their move yet,
but there have been some
unsettling chi disturbances.
What do you mean
by "unsettling"?
Historically, Kyoto
is a city built on balance.
It was designed
using the sacred principals
of both feng shui
and onmyoudou.
Because of that,
there are several power spots
scattered around the city.
However, the chi
from those spots
has been redirected
towards Nijo Castle.
So, what do you think's
gonna happen then?
It's hard to say right now.
but I don't get the feeling
it's anything good.
Anyway, here's the plan.
Everyone in the Sitri family
is on standby.
Guard the Kyoto area.
[GROUP]
Right.
[AZAZEL] The Gremory family
and Irina will be our offense.
You'll head to Nijo Castle.
[GROUP]
Right.
Saving Princess Yasaka
should definitely
be our highest priority.
We have no idea
what Cao Cao is capable of,
so I won't be
sending you out alone.
I've called in
someone to help
who is pretty good at handling
these types of situations.
You did?
Who is it then?
Well, I'd rather
not ruin the surprise,
but you'll know them
when you see them.
In the meantime, just focus
on holding your ground
until they get there.
Some good and bad news.
I was able to get
two vials of Phoenix Tears,
but unfortunately,
that's all I could round up.
‐Just two?
‐But that won't be enough.
I'm sorry, everyone,
it's the best I could manage.
Each group gets one,
so use it wisely.
And one more thing.
‐Listen, Saji.
‐[SAJI] Yes?
I want you to go
with the Gremory Family.
‐[SAJI] Uh...
‐Your dragon king form.
It might prove to be useful.
So, I need you there
to support Issei.
But, sir‐‐
[AZAZEL] Issei,
that makes you responsible
for bringing Saji back
if he goes out of control.
Right.
You sure?
After all the shit you gave me
back during the Sitri game,
I'd much rather
have you as an ally.
Don't worry,
I've got your back on this one.
Thanks, Issei.
One final note before we go.
It's regarding
the Hero Faction.
We've got devils, angels,
fallen angels and yokai.
They've come from all over
to help us defeat Cao Cao.
We'll make sure they're
each in place for the attack.
Don't you worry,
if any baddies try to escape,
we'll make sure
to punish them!
I think that's everything.
Once we're finished
with preparations,
you should head for your
designated locations.
I will be supervising
the battle from here.
I can't go with you.
So, don't you dare die on me.
This trip isn't over until
everyone makes it back home.
Protect Kyoto and yourselves.
Got it?
[GROUP]
Yes.
[low rumbling]
[GASPER] Wow,
that was really tough.
To think, members of
the Old Satan Faction got in.
It's hard to believe.
‐[KONEKO] You cool, Rias?
‐[RIAS] Hmm?
‐[RIAS] I feel a little uneasy.
‐[KONEKO gasps]
Why? Do you sense a douchebag?
I think it's...
about Issei.
Rightfully so.
I mean, he's off in Kyoto
surrounded by
tons of innocent, cute girls
and you're stuck here.
‐[AKENO giggles]
‐[KONEKO] I'm worried.
Issei! Hey!
Yeah?
You need me?
Seems there's been
an incident.
Another molester struck
right outside the hotel.
I happened
to be passing by
so I helped detain
the perv responsible.
Afterwards,
this popped out of his body.
Recognize it?
[DDRAIG]
It can't be.
What is it, Ddraig?
[DDRAIG]
Believe it or not,
that's the thing
that jumped out of you
back on the bullet train.
It's what was in the box.
[gasps]
[ISSEI] Are you kidding me?
This is my potential?!
Yep. Makes sense.
When I examined the object,
it definitely had
a very Issei feel.
[DDRAIG]
Yes, it seems so.
But wait.
How very strange.
‐[ISSEI] What is?
‐[DDRAIG] Your potential.
It seems that
it traveled around Kyoto
by jumping
from person to person,
using them as vessels to grab
every available boob
it could along the way.
[screams]
Issei's potential
was the culprit
behind all
the molester cases,
so in a way I guess
it was an epidemic.
[SAJI gasping]
No way!
[AZAZEL]
Interesting.
What can the perv‐orb do?
[DDRAIG]
No idea,
but I can sense that
it possesses a strong power.
[AZAZEL chuckles]
Basically, thanks to Issei,
we'll have to follow up
on the molesters.
Great. It's not like
I have anything better to do.
[ISSEI] Sorry
my potential is a horn dog.
[ROSSWEISSE gags]
[ISSEI]
Huh?
[ROSSWEISSE gagging]
And there she goes.
How is there anything left?
[ROSSWEISSE retching]
Hmm? What's wrong?
Just inner turmoil.
Like questioning my existence.
I was wondering
what makes somebody a hero.
When I was a human,
heroes were people
that I worshiped.
But these days,
I'm not so certain.
[AZAZEL]
Really?
Let me get this straight.
You think you can't be a hero
because you just happen
to be a devil?
Listen. What do you want to be?
It's up to you.
Duh, a high‐ranking devil
and the Harem King, obviously!
Ha, but seriously,
for right now I just want
to work hard for the prez
and all my friends.
It's a pretty decent goal.
As long as that's
what you want.
It's important to remain
true to yourself.
[chuckles]
I hear ya.
I won't let you down!
Tonight, we're gonna kick
some Hero Faction ass.
‐[ISSEI grunts]
‐[KUNOU] Surprise!
Kunou! What are you doing?
I'm helping you.
I don't know.
This all seems
a little dangerous
for a teensy fox.
I want to be the one
to save Mother!
Please! I won't leave!
You can't make me!
[GROUP chuckles]
Fine. You can come then.
Who knows?
A nine‐tail like yourself
might come in handy.
[KUNOU giggles]
‐[wind blowing]
‐[KUNOU gasps]
[wind whistling]
[KUNOU]
It's the fog.
Looks like we're in
a dimensional space again.
‐[phone buzzing]
‐Oh!
What's up, Kiba?
Where you at?
[KIBA on phone] We're at
the Kyoto Imperial Palace.
Rossweisse and Saji
are with me. You?
Kunou and I are on a subway
platform at Kyoto Station.
[KIBA] Do you want to try
and meet up at Nijo Castle?
‐Yeah, sure.
‐[KIBA] Okay.
Can you contact Asia
and the others?
Leave it to me.
[KIBA] Oh, and Issei?
Since Rias isn't here right now,
that makes you our king.
[ISSEI gasps]
[KIBA] You proved it
back on Togetsukyo Bridge.
The only reason
we made it out safely
is because you were there
to guide us.
That's why we're counting
on you again tonight.
[chuckles] I'll try.
[ISSEI]
Asia? Yeah.
Be careful.
It's okay.
Asia said on the phone that
the church trio are together.
[KUNOU]
Thank goodness! What a relief!
[DDRAIG]
Welsh Dragon!
Balance Breaker!
[squeals happily]
[KUNOU giggles]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Kunou.
I promise we're gonna
go save your mom,
but you gotta stay
in my sights at all times, okay?
I'll do my best
to protect you.
'Kay, I shall remain
here beside you.
‐[low growling]
‐[KUNOU gasps]
Hello there.
It's been a while.
I'm guessing
you don't remember me.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Uh, we've met?
[SHADOW USER]
I'm not surprised.
I'm just another
"nameless lackey."
Utterly forgettable
after one fight.
[inaudible]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
I remember now.
You had a Sacred Gear
that could control shadows!
I'm touched you remember,
but this time
I'm gonna show you
what a shadow user
can really do!
Balance Break!
[shadows surging]
[growling]
[grunts]
[SHADOW USER‐JUGGERNAUT]
What do you think?
I look like you, right?
I admired your armor so much
the last time we fought,
I decided I wanted
a set of my own.
So, I went on a field trip
and obtained
Night Reflection Death Cross.
Now, then.
You and I have
unfinished business.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Bring it on!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT grunts]
[grunting]
[SHADOW USER‐JUGGERNAUT
snickers]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT yells]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT groans]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT grunting]
♪
[SHADOW USER‐JUGGERNAUT]
Looks like you're stuck...
Red Dragon Emperor.
[grunts]
[ISSEI]
"My potential released!"