[ISSEI]
Summon!
Tig ole Bitties!
[serene music plays]
[gasps]
Whoa. Rias?
Uh, what's going on?
Whoa. Hold on.
Where am I?
Did you summon me?
To Kyoto?
‐Give 'em a poke.
‐[ISSEI gasps]
[ELSHA]
Poke those pillows. Do it.
[gasps]
[ISSEI] Wait. Like in front
of all these people?
[ELSHA]
Yes, poke them...
like you've never poked before.
You know, "Boop!"
[ISSEI]
I've never said "Boop!"
So why the hell
would I start now?
[ELSHA]
Rias Gremory's nips are crucial.
They're a switch, so to speak.
[ISSEI]
Sorry, you lost me after "nips."
[ELSHA]
Specifically, they're the switch
to unlock your potential.
[ISSEI]
Wait, are you saying
those sweet little saucers
are like cheat code buttons
that'll activate
my ultimate God Mode?
[ELSHA]
Crude, but yes, that's the gist.
[ISSEI gasps]
[RIAS]
Uh, why am I glowing?
[ELSHA] Now that her boobs
have come into contact
with your potential,
they have evolved.
They're ready for you.
[ISSEI gasps]
That's the most beautiful thing
I've ever heard.
[ELSHA]
If you jab those jugs,
it'll cause dramatic changes
within you.
[ISSEI] It'll cause
dramatic changes in my pants.
[moans]
[gasps]
Okay, then.
I think I finally understand
what needs to be done.
Here goes!
Issei?
So hey,
mind if I poke your bazongas?
[gasps]
[laughs]
[whimpers]
Huh. Of all the things
to say right now.
But, for you, I guess
it makes sense. Go ahead.
All right!
[giggles]
[grunts]
Are you ready
to do this, Ddraig?
[DDRAIG weeping]
[whispers]
Jeez calm down. Baby.
Boop time!
[screams]
[screaming continues]
You're welcome?
Okay, sure. Makes sense.
Uhh...
‐[gasping]
‐[heartbeat thudding]
[ELSHA]
This is it! Get ready!
[ISSEI] I've never felt such
a hardcore power level before!
[gasps]
But, somehow, it feels familiar
[DDRAIG]
Yes. It's magnificent, isn't it?
This power brings back
strong memories.
This energy,
it feels like my original aura,
back when I still had
my old body,
when I wanted to win
against the White Dragon!
[dramatic music plays]
[gasps] Huh?
Congratulations, the door to
your potential has been opened.
Thanks, Elsha.
It's all because of you.
You convinced me to embrace
my identity as a total perv.
Loving boobs really pays off.
You're very welcome.
And now,
having unlocked your potential,
it's time for us to go.
This is goodbye, Issei.
Goodbye? You mean like forever?
Indeed. The remnants of our
feelings kept us here.
But there's no longer
a reason for us to stay.
‐We can finally be free.
‐No, wait!
What about all
the good times we've had?
Look, it's not you, it's me.
I'm just not a boob person.
That's more your specialty.
You're the only guy I know
that uses tatas to power up.
You'll be perfectly fine.
Besides, you've got Ddraig
and your friends to help you.
Now, why don't you
go raise some hell?
[gasps]
Elsha. I‐‐
I know, what if Belzard
were to give you
a few words of advice
before we leave you?
[gasps]
You're Belzard?
Grabbin' Dragon.
Tail a‐waggin'.
Likes boobs "A" to triple "G."
‐[gasps]
‐[chuckles]
Yes, very well said, Belzard.
Now then,
we should probably get going.
[gasps]
That wasn't well said!
He didn't actually say anything!
Those are just lyrics from the
stupid "Grabbin' Dragon" song!
Fine, whatever. I'm outta here.
Okay, asswipes, feel the wrath
of my perv power!
Let's do this! Boosted Gear!
This energy's mind‐blowing!
Like it's coming at me
from every direction:
the bottom, the inside,
and the Sacred Gear!
Damn, Ddraig, you've got
some serious power, bro!
[DDRAIG]
Yes, it's been a while
since I've been able
to fully access all of it.
[ISSEI]
I get it. The Juggernaut drive
was an uncontrolled release
of this power,
but thanks to Elsha, I can
finally tap into it on my own!
Oh, great. What's this?
It's potential!
It's mine and Ddraig's, too.
It's the potential
of our future together!
Mode Change:
Welsh Blaster Bishop!
[grunts]
Get ready, gutter sluts!
You're gonna pay
for what you did to my friends!
[DDRAIG]
Boost! Boost! Boost!
[ISSEI]
You made me feel weak,
like there was nothing
I could do,
but now I'm gonna
make you eat those feelings
like a teen doing
the Tide POD challenge!
‐[DDRAIG] Boost!
‐[ISSEI] Take this!
Dragon Blaster!
Aw, hell yeah!
‐Move!
‐[grunts]
[grunts]
No way.
[SIEGFRIED]
His power's incredible.
He even warped the dimension.
[ISSEI]
I'm just getting started.
Cao Cao!
Mode Change:
Welsh Sonic Boost Knight!
‐And now, Armor Purge!
‐[DDRAIG] Boost! Boost! Boost!
Boost! Boost! Boost!
[grunts]
‐[coughs]
‐[ISSEI] Mode Change:
Welsh Draconic Rook!
[grunts]
‐[gasps]
‐[DDRAIG] Boost!
[ISSEI]
Come on, Ddraig!
Let's show this taint goblin
what happens
when you decide to mess
with the Grabbin' Dragon!
‐[DDRAIG] Boost!
‐[grunts]
Later, doucher!
[ISSEi grunts, pants]
‐Damn, Ddraig, we are savage!
‐[DDRAIG] Indeed.
The power released
as the Red Dragon Emperor,
along with the Evil Piece
inside you,
allows you to promote
yourself without a King.
Yeah, but it's
a huge ass power drain.
At this rate, I'll only be able
to maintain the armor
a little bit longer.
[gasps]
Well, you certainly
pulled that trick
out of your hat
at the last minute.
I probably would have died
if it weren't for this spear.
However, that little stunt
looked like an Illegal Move.
[ISSEI laughs]
Just like your mom.
Yes, that's very mature.
Actually, it's a well‐known
chess term.
An Illegal Move means
an unacceptable play,
and I say that
because all of your attacks
deviate from
the Evil Piece system.
[DDRAIG] I personally felt
like it was more of a Triaina.
[ISSEI]
Whatty what now?
[DDRAIG] Triaina.
It's the three‐pronged trident
that was used
by the Greek god Poseidon.
The transformations
you just used
also came in a set of threes
and displayed the same power
of the god's trident.
[ISSEI] Yeah, that sounds
pretty bitchin'.
From this day forward,
that play shall be known
as "Illegal Move Triaina"!
Congratulations.
However, it looks
like you're low on juice.
[ISSEI]
What a tool.
Last time
we caught him off‐guard,
but now the dude's
gonna be watching us.
What's wrong, Cao Cao?
Why don't you come open
this can of whoop ass?
Well, I would,
but there's not much to open.
Besides, it looks
like we're out of time.
[ISSEI gasps]
That's not good.
It seems our guest
has finally arrived.
Hey, Georg! Be a dear
and prepare to summon
the Dragon Eater.
[gasps]
Wait, this isn't right!
This chi. It's the
Mischievous Dragon, Yu‐Long!
[ISSEI] Yu‐Long? Isn't that
one of the five dragon kings?
[man]
Geronimo! Ho‐ho!
If it isn't the young
spear‐wielding whipper snapper!
[CAO CAO]
Oh, and if it isn't
the Great Victorious
Fighting Buddha.
Pray tell, to what
do I owe this pleasure?
Don't play dumb, you know why
I'm here you little shit‐stain.
This prank of yours
has gone too far,
and while some heroes
rise up to become deities,
others end up
becoming the poison
that gives everyone else
a bad name.
Did that answer your question
or should I use smaller words?
Well, sonny?
"Poison"? I see.
If you're the one
labeling me as poison,
then I think I'll
take that as a compliment.
Hm! Leave the rest to me.
I'm the first‐generation
Sun Wukong.
[ISSEI] Whoa! No shit?
That's super awesome!
Ya did real good, kiddo.
I'll handle things from here.
Yu‐long, take care
of the fox broad!
[YU‐LONG]
Got it.
Hey. Not to rain
on your parade,
but it looks like Vritra
beat us to the punch.
[SUN WUKONG] Not yet,
he hasn't. Go lend him a claw.
After this,
you can gorge yourself
with the best Kyoto
cuisine around.
[YU‐LONG]
No take backsies!
Ahh.
All right, all right, all right!
Dragon King,
coming in hot!
Well, then, back
to these turd sandwiches.
Fool!
Extend Staff!
[grunts, screams]
[JEANNE gasps]
Your back wasn't even in it.
Maybe you need
some more training.
[grunts]
Oh, heavenly path, hear me!
come down
with a clap of thunder
through the jaws of a dragon.
‐Lay upon the land.
‐[clangs]
‐[gasps]
‐[YASAKA growls]
Well, would ya look at that?
The dragons are
almost done over there.
Without that four‐eyes' spell,
the fox is running
on empty. Huh?
[chuckles]
Oh dear.
You seem to have
given me a teensy prick,
but then again you know
all about those, don't you?
I'm glad to see you're as
healthy and disgusting as ever.
[SIEGFRIED]
Cao Cao, we should retreat!
Yes, I suppose.
[ISSEI grunts]
[CAO CAO] Sorry to leave
the party so early.
Oh no, you don't!
Just one attack.
I just want one attack
to reach that goocher!
Technically, I'm supposed
to be doling out
the punishments,
but give it a shot.
[ISSEI]
Suck on this!
Turn, dammit!
‐[grunts]
‐[ISSEI] Yes!
[both gasp]
[grunts]
Dragon Emperor!
That's it!
Spear! Holy spear that
can even pierce the gods.
The ideals of the king
of domination that sleeps‐‐
Cao Cao, don't!
This is not the time
to show Truth Idea.
Besides, we still
need to get Leonardo.
Yes, I'm aware.
Red Dragon Emperor!
Or should I say,
Issei Hyodo.
You had better get stronger.
Stronger than Vali.
When you do that,
then I'll show you
the true power
of my Longinus.
[crying]
Oh, Mother. Please wake up.
Hey, kid, don't you have
the special ability
to talk to a woman's
Humpty Dumplings?
Uh, yeah.
You mean Boobielingual?
[SUN WUKONG]
I think I've got an idea.
I'll help you, but see
if you can use that spell
on the little lady
and the mama fox youkai
‐at the same time.
‐[ISSEI] I'll give it a shot.
Boobielingual!
Okay then, munchkin.
See if you can
get through to your mother.
Mother? It's me.
I'm here with you.
Please turn back to normal,
I beg of you! [sobs]
I'll never ask you
for anything again, I promise.
So... please...
please change back
to the mother I know and love.
‐[sobbing]
‐[YASAKA] My... daughter.
Mother! Yes, it's me!
You have to come back!
I've missed you terribly,
and I've been so worried!
Please, all I want is for us
to walk the streets
of Kyoto. I'll do anything!
[gasps]
She did it!
‐Am I...?
‐[KUNOU] You're back!
[sobbing]
Mother's here now.
You know, a princess
shouldn't cry so much.
[crying]
‐[sobbing continues]
[YASAKA]
Sir Azazel, Red Dragon Emperor,
as well as all
of the Gremory Family.
Words cannot express
how grateful we are to you.
We're in your debt.
After your departure,
I have arranged to meet
with both the Great Victorious
Fighting Buddha Sun Wukong
and Lady Leviathan.
It is my sincerest wish
to cooperate with everyone,
so that Kyoto will
never again be in a situation
such as the one we found
ourselves in last night.
I'm right there with you.
We'll all do our best.
[giggles] The fox youkai have
offered to show me
around Kyoto a bit more before
we have our meeting later.
But I hope that the rest
of you have a safe trip back.
After all,
the trip doesn't end...
Until everyone's home.
[KUNOU]
Red Dragon Emperor!
You can just call me Issei.
Uh... okay, Issei.
Will you come and visit
us in Kyoto again?
Yeah. I'd love to.
I'm so excited!
And next time you can try
Mother's boiled tofu!
Yep!
[man on P. A.] Nozomi 24,
outbound to Tokyo, will soon
‐be departing the station.
‐Thanks for seeing us off!
‐Next time we'll bring everyone!
‐[KUNOU] Goodbye!
Thank you again for everything
you've done for us!
I won't forget it!
Promise me you'll
come back soon, okay!
Fo sho! See ya later, Kunou!
Stay outta trouble!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Ah! Son of a bitch!
What? Is something
the matter, Issei?
I forgot to ask Yasaka
to show me
her foxy footballs
for saving her!
Oh, cruel world,
how could you do this to me?
Damn, that mofo's trippin'
like nobody's business!
Ya know, I bet it's
because we never
‐got to have our porno party!
‐[grumbles]
All right, fap‐masters,
sit down before I report you!
Gah, you're a bunch
of depraved dill‐holes.
You should have told us
what happened, Issei!
‐Uh, yeah.
‐And you said
that you were
going to contact us
after Kinkakuji,
but we never heard
back from you.
That's right.
Thanks for nothing, loser.
Well, what really matters
is that everyone
got home safe and sound.
[AZAZEL]
Plus, you can't blame the kid,
he had his hands full
with a new woman.
I guess you could
say she was a real fox.
Hey, shut it, Azazel!
And if that was supposed to be
a clever pun, it sucked balls!
Know what? I imagine
that the little fox princess
may very well inherit
her mother's good looks,
as well as few other assets.
What the eff, Azazel?
Gross, dude.
Besides, I prefer her mom's
ample motorboating material.
‐[punches]
‐[weakly] What'd I say?
You know, cockmuppet.
Besides, Issei finally managed
to unlock
his potential in Kyoto,
so cut him some slack.
Well, I suppose that's
a good development.
Then again,
he did poke my boobs.
About that! Sorry for summoning
you in your skivvies!
But thanks for letting me
jab your jawbreakers!
[sighs]
Anyway. Thanks to Issei
we had to follow up
on all the molesters.
But at least now the school
trip is finally over. [gags]
[AZAZEL] And next up
is the school festival.
By the way, I've got some news
about the daughter
of the Phoenix family.
She'll be transferring
to your school soon.
You mean Ravel? For real?
That's right. Apparently,
she was pretty impressed
by Rias and Sitri and decided
she wants to study in Japan.
She's a first‐year student,
kind of like Koneko, I believe.
She can suck it.
It feels kind of sudden,
though. Wonder why.
Well, things are rough
for everyone, y'know?
Moving along.
I'm happy nobody died
and that you all had
a good time in Kyoto,
but now we've got
the Rating Game
with Sairaorg to worry about.
There're still
a lot of preparations
‐that need to be made.
‐[GROUP] Right!
[ISSEI] Oh yeah.
The upcoming Rating Game.
I'll get to face off
against Sairaorg again.
And this time I'll win!
[grunting]
[SEIGVAIRA]
Sairaorg, have you heard?
‐Huh?
‐There's a rumor
that the Red Dragon Emperor
of the Gremory household
has obtained
a special new ability.
That sounds pretty interesting.
[SEIGVAIRA] They say that
he fought against the leader
of the Hero Faction,
against the possessor
of the True Longinus
and survived.
No surprise. After all,
dying would only break
his promise to me.
Right. Bring it on,
Issei Hyodo!
[ISSEI] We're preparing
for the school festival!