Future? You think
you can show us?
Yeah, son! Chill, I've got this.
Or, you know what?
We'll show 'em together!
[gasps]
Huh?
Your armor. That's impossible.
♪
‐‐[CROWD cheers]
‐‐[NAUD] Oh, wow!
The Red Dragon Emperor was
enveloped in a bright red light!
Not only is he back on his feet,
but he appears to
be as good as new!
What could have caused such
a drastic transformation?
Look at the color of his aura.
It's the same shade of
crimson as Rias' hair.
The same as the woman he loves.
[DDRAIG] Issei. It would seem
most of the curse is gone.
[ISSEI] Yeah, some old
Albion dude helped me out.
[DDRAIG] I see. And now
you've somehow managed
to use the power of
the Red Dragon Emperor
to promote yourself
to a Queen.
[ISSEI] No way. Guess that makes
me the new Boss Bitch, baby.
Well, it looks like you
actually pulled off
a Cardinal Crimson Promotion.
Not surprising, since red is
the color of the Gremory house.
[RIAS gasps]
[ISSEI] Listen up! Today I'm
fighting for my dreams!
And for the dreams
of the children!
And for the dreams of
the Gremory Family!
You're goin' down!
Because... Because...
Aw, shit! Because...!
[ISSEI] ...I'm in love
with Rias Gremory!
[CROWD cheers]
[laughs]
Way to go, kid, that
took balls. Alright then!
It's time to finish
this Rating Game,
so charge at me
with all you've got!
[ISSEI]
Here comes the pain!
[DDRAIG] Super Sonic Booster!
Solid Impact Booster!
[ISSEI, SAIRAORG grunting]
[NAUD]
It's a fist fight!
They're just going toe‐to‐toe
like a couple of rambunctious
children in the school yard!
Except there are no teachers
around to break up the fight,
the school yard is being
completely destroyed,
and their punches are
strong enough to explode
an ordinary man's skull like
a drop‐kicked blowup doll!
[shouts]
[ISSEI groans]
[DDRAIG]
Listen!
Your body hasn't had time to
adjust the Queen form yet!
At this rate, our Balance
Breaker is going to deactivate!
[ISSEI] We're just gonna
have to deal with it!
[ISSEI]
This roid‐freak's going down!
Suck on this!
[DDRAIG]
Solid Impact Booster!
[SAIRAORG groans]
[SAIRAORG grunts]
[SAIRAORG]
Why are my legs shaking?
This is just the beginning.
No way. I'll enjoy this
battle to the fullest.
[grunts]
I have to keep going.
Otherwise, I don't deserve
my place in the underworld
as a member of the Bael Family.
I must not fail!
So much willpower. But...
...this pussy is
about to get poached.
[SAIRAORG shouts]
[SAIRAORG grunts]
[ISSEI]
Here goes... Crimson Blaster!
[DDRAIG]
Fang Blast Booster!
[ISSEI]
Money Shot!
[SAIRAORG grunts]
[ISSEI gasps]
[ISSEI]
Holy shit! It can't be!
Arise.
[SAIRAORG grunts]
Get up. You must be strong!
This isn't the end
for you, Sairaorg.
[grunts]
[MISLA] You fight for the
sake of the underworld,
and so that no other
will have to experience
what you went through.
That's the future
you want to see.
A world where skill
and hard work,
not what someone was born to be,
is what is truly valued.
Isn't that what's driving you?
My dearest Sairaorg.
Please make your
dream come true.
Create the world
that you desire!
[SAIRAORG grunts, yells]
[SAIRAORG yells]
[SAIRAORG]
Now then, Issei Hyodo.
For the sake of all my goals,
this is where you are defeated!
[ISSEI]
Bring it on, bitch!
[SAIRAORG shouts]
[ISSEI shouts]
[ISSEI] He's taken so much
damage, but he's still going.
Vali and Cao Cao were powerful
shits, too, but there's an
F‐cup‐sized difference
between him and those dudes.
They're not even in
the same league!
He'll stop at nothing
to curb stomp my ass.
He thinks that if he loses,
he won't have another chance.
So he'll die here
if he needs to.
He's put everything into
this wet dream of his.
Which means there's
absolutely no way
the dude's backing down.
He's an ass‐kicking automaton!
[SAIRAORG]
This game is all I have.
If I lose here, I lose my life.
Everything I've built up to
this point will fall apart.
For someone who wasn't
born with demonic power,
this is my only path
to victory. My single chance.
So I'll fight until my
knuckles are bloody,
and you can see the
white of my bones.
It may seem uncool to you,
but that's all I can do.
[ISSEI] He's incredible.
I think I'm hard.
I can't even put his
amazingness into actual words.
Which is exactly why
I'll keep fighting.
I want to defeat a man like you!
[ISSEI]
I have a dream, too.
I want to make the President
the King of this game.
And then become a king myself.
Meaning...
...I'll be the strongest
pawn in existence!
Eat fist, douche!
[ISSEI] Still not enough?
How much do I have left?
I'm so drained.
[ISSEI exhales] I'll go on as
long as I can clench my fists.
I'll do it for her.
[REGULUS] Red Dragon Emperor.
That's enough.
[ISSEI gasps]
[REGULUS]
My master. Lord Sairaorg.
[ISSEI gasps]
[REGULUS]
Can't you see?
It's too late. He's already
lost consciousness.
[ISSEI gasps]
[REGULUS] Even so,
he was genuinely happy.
He rushed forward...
without hesitation.
He truly enjoyed fighting you,
putting his dream on the line.
[REGULUS whimpers]
In the end, he was
fighting out of sheer will.
Even though he was knocked out,
he never paused.
He moved forward...
toward his goal.
[ISSEI] Thank you.
You totally insane badass!
[CROWD cheers]
[NAUD]
Sairaorg Bael has resigned.
Rias Gremory is the official
winner of the Rating Game!
[ISSEI grunts]
Are you awake?
[gasps]
Is everything over?
It was a good fight. Maybe the
first time in my entire life
I've ever been
satisfied by losing.
Although, honestly, I don't
really remember the end of it.
There's only one
thing I'm sure about.
That was the best
battle I ever had.
Same here, bro. And I
feel great right now.
Am I interrupting something?
[ISSEI]
Whoa, Sir Zechs!
[SIR ZECHS] No, please.
Don't get up on my account.
Listen, Issei. Sairaorg.
That was truly incredible.
The higher‐ups are
more than satisfied.
That battle has everyone
expecting great things
from the both of you.
Sairaorg, if you please.
May I take a moment to
speak about Issei's future?
Yes, of course.
I can see myself out.
No need. I want you
to hear this as well.
Issei. There's been some
talk of promoting you
to a mid‐ranking devil.
[ISSEI gasps] You're not just
jerkin' me off here, are you?
I'm not. To be precise,
you, Kiba, and Akeno
would be promoted.
[gasps]
You still have much to learn,
Grabbin' Dragon.
But everyone is invested
in what you do from now on.
Accept this fate, Issei Hyodo.
[ISSEI gasps]
I believe that you'll become a
mighty hero of the underworld.
[gasps]
[SIR ZECHS chuckles]
Well, I'll explain the
details at a later time.
For now, I'll take my leave.
A promotion is great,
but you should think
about someone else.
Tell me, how is Rias doing?
[gasps]
Seems like the perfect time to
tell her your feelings again.
[ISSEI grunts]
Get her alone and tell
her what's in your heart,
face‐to‐face.
It's the only way you'll know
if she feels the same way.
You've already shown
courage today. Why stop now?
Dammit. This sucks!
What if she totally
steps on my heart?
If she does, you can
come back to me.
I'll hook you up with
a stiff drink or two.
You can cry all you want.
Thank you so much, Sairaorg.
Sorry I thought you
were a dickhole.
[ISSEI sobs]
Feelings are the worst.
[SAIRAORG chuckles]
[CROWD chatters]
Welcome everyone to the
mansion of the Occult.
'Kay, say cheese!
Here, that was a good one!
Oh my gosh. Thanks so much!
[chattering]
[ISSEI] The President dressed
as a waitress. Ha. ha. ha!
It's so hot that my cockpit's
getting cramped.
‐‐Issei?
‐‐Huh?
Hey, it's your turn to
scare the customers.
I'm on it!
Rawr!
[GIRL A screams] It's a
fugly perv‐monster! Run away!
‐‐[GIRLS scream]
‐‐[ISSEI] Huh?
[GIRLS]
He's so cute!
Boo, I'm so scary!
Um, I'm gonna get you!
Leave it to Gasper to be the
least threatening vampire ever.
[KATASE]
Ah‐hah! There he is!
We're gonna beat the
perversity outta you.
Here goes!
[KATASE, MURAYAMA]
Get him!
[ISSEI yells, grunts]
Ow, ow, ow!
Well. Fuck me.
Uh?
[ISSEI]
Seriously?
The guys who were backing
Sairaorg just pulled out like a
dude on prom night?
[AZAZEL]
The higher ups value talent.
That's how it works
when you're a devil.
If you can't cut it, then
there are consequences.
But what about his seat
as heir to the Bael Family?
[AZAZEL chuckles] I can assure
you that much hasn't changed.
Even with his loss, Sairaorg is
still powerful, and popular too.
That's not something
they can take away.
Oh, I guess that's cool then.
You should probably worry
more about yourself.
After all, you've got
your own problems.
Don't forget about
your new Queen form.
You need to start thinking
about how to level that up.
Right!
[MATSUDA]
Issei! Yo, where you at, playa?
Well, sounds like
you're needed.
[MATSUDA]
There he is!
Hey, we got a mad bone to
pick with yo scrawny ass!
They friggin' black balled
us from your fun‐filled,
fun bag café, you gots
to help a brotha out!
Yeah, the bro code states
you have to help us
sneak in somehow!
[ISSEI grunts]
Dude, the bro code always ends
with a wicked ass kicking!
‐‐[door clatters]
‐‐[RIAS gasps]
Issei?
[ISSEI]
Uh, hey there.
You did good work
out there today.
Thanks. Whatcha doin?
Oh, I was just thinking.
You know, since this is
my last festival and all.
[ISSEI]
Hm...
Just get her alone and tell
her what's in your heart.
[ISSEI] C'mon dude, grow a
pair already. Tell her.
Tell her all that junk
you've been hiding.
And then, call her by name
instead of that stupid
"Prez" shit.
She deserves that much.
[ISSEI grunts]
Hey, Rias.
[gasps]
Huh?
I wanna protect you for the
rest of our lives together.
[gasps]
Because well, the truth is,
I've been in love with
you for a long time!
[RIAS gasps, whimpers]
[gasps]
I'm okay! It's just...
I'm really happy.
[ISSEI gasps]
It's been so long since
you said my name.
You had me worried that... that
I would never hear it again.
I waited so long.
But then you said
all that at the game,
and it made me happy.
I didn't expect
to hear it then.
It caught me by surprise.
You drive me crazy. I never
know what do with you.
So... what's that mean for us?
Do you feel the same way, maybe?
[RIAS]
Issei... Listen I...
I should have said
something sooner.
I do love you.
More than anyone else.
[ALL yelp]
[RIAS, ISSE gasp]
[KIBA]
Yep, that kinda hurt.
Hey! What the hell?
Uh, hi! Congratulations to
the both of you!
I'm positive that you'll have
many happy years together.
And I'm positive this
won't stop me from trying
to procreate with you.
And I'm positive that I can
probably convince Issei
to cheat on you with me.
Basically, the future's gonna
be a ho‐down throw‐down.
Uh. You can count me out.
You guys are, like, so cute!
I suppose I can allow
your crazy teenage hormones
to go wild just for today.
Get outta here!
This isn't an orgy!
For real!
You have no idea how long
I've been waiting for this one
special moment, you could at
least give us a little privacy!
[BOTH gasp]
This is all your fault, Issei!
You should have confessed
somewhere more secluded.
[ISSEI gasps]
How was I supposed to know?
[ALL]
Just take responsibility, Issei.
[ISSEI]
Huh?
[IRINA, XENOVIA giggle]
Time for the romantic kiss!
[ISSEI, RIAS gasp]
[ISSEI, RIAS chuckle]
[ISSEI]
Rias.
[RIAS]
Issei.
[SAIRAORG]
How's Issei doin' these days?
[AZAZEL] Good, he finally manned
up and confessed to Rias.
You know, I really do
think those two kids
are a good fit in the long run.
I'm surprised you're worried
about others right now.
You're a pretty decent guy Lord
Sairaorg, through and through.
[SAIRAORG]
Heh.
So then, back to
square one, huh?
I'm used to these
kind of things.
It's honestly no big deal.
Can you believe Issei was
concerned about your status?
Please tell him this for me:
I'm gonna be back on top.
My Lord Sairaorg!
[SAIRAORG gasps]
[NURSES gasp]
[DOCTOR A gasps]
Mother?
[SAIRAORG gasps]
Mother!
It's Sairaorg, please say
that you recognize me.
I do. You're my dearest son.
[SAIRAORG gasps]
Oh Sairaorg, look how
strong you've become.
In my dreams, I felt
like I watched you grow,
not only as a man
but as a person.
I'm so proud of you, darling.
I've missed you so much.
[SAIRAORG sobs]
Mother. Let's go home. Together.
[AZAZEL]
I have a sneaking suspicion
who created this miracle.
It had to be Boobielingual.
There's no other explanation.
The Grabbin Dragon
strikes again.
He manages to get through even
the thickest personal bubbles.
I wonder how far his
naiveté will reach?
I'm interested to see
what he'll do next.
[AZAZEL] Lord Sakra!
May I have a word?
Yo. 'Sup, Fallen Angel
of Justice?
[AZAZEL] Cut the crap,
you knew about Cao Cao
before we did, didn't you?
[SAKRA]
Heh. Can you be more specific?
I've known him since he was
a pint‐sized little brat.
Why do ya care so much?
Dammit, Indra!
[SAKRA laughs] I can't
believe you called me that,
looks like baby Azazel's balls
have dropped, am I right?
[AZAZEL grunts]
Hey, listen.
It's in a God's nature to
spout out stupid ideals while
doing whatever they
please in the shadows.
So you're just gonna have
to get off your high horse.
Yes, I'm aware. However...
[SAKRA] Fine, just chill out,
I'll throw you a friggin' bone.
It is true that Orphis
has become a problem.
In return, give that Tit
Dragon a message for me.
Tell him I think he's
a total bad ass.
And that if he does
get outta line,
that I have no problem
whatsoever destroying
what's left of his
decrepit soul.
Cause the label of heaven
is only available to us.