[sighs]
So, I definitely think
that Bishop form is gonna be
the biggest beeyatch
of the whole Triaina combo.
Probably. Unlike the Knight
and the Rook,
the Bishop form needs additional
time to charge the blast.
[ISSEI]
Yeah, and it'd be hella obvious
if we just stood there
the whole time.
[grunts, shouts]
It sounds kind of corny,
but we could use teamwork.
Yeah, fo sho.
If the team buys me time,
I could get a better shot.
Then I won't have to worry about
all that bobbing
and weaving crap
while I charge up the attack.
Sucks the Triaina saps energy
faster than streaming porn
off of WiFi.
I'll be lucky to get
a couple of shots in
before I've blown my whole load.
[KIBA]
If we're gonna use it,
it'd be best to save it
for Sairaorg.
[ISSEI]
Yeah. Sho ‘nuff.
[explosion]
[XENOVIA]
Oops, my bad!
[ROSSWEISSE] Let's take
a quick break for right now.
[XENOVIA]
All right, sounds good!
‐[groans]
‐Hey, are you okay?
‐Yeah.
‐Sorry, I couldn't help
‐but overhear your conversation.
‐Oh?
What you said about
the Bishop form in the Triaina.
It's only a suggestion...
but instead
of a full‐on cannon blast,
couldn't you just
transfer the shot?
Both:
That's a great idea!
That way
your team can give cover fire
in a more effective way.
If we can make it look like
a charge and boost our allies,
then we could take them
by surprise. It could work.
Not to mention it'll leave
our frenemies hanging
on whether the next cannon blast
is gonna be a transfer
or an attack!
[RIAS]
True,
but we may have some
trouble with the game rules.
‐We will?
‐It won't be a concern
as long as the match
is a team battle.
Sairaorg stated previously
that he would like to accept
all of our various powers
in a single fight.
The higher‐ups involved
have approved this request.
And because of those
particular concessions,
I believe they'll make
special rules for the match.
"Special rules," huh?
Like what?
To start. They intend
to hold the Rating Game
inside a floating city,
which is over in the domain
of Archduke Agares's family.
And, they're planning to invite
a rather large audience,
so that means they're probably
not expecting it
to be a very long battle.
The Rating Game is just
another form of entertainment,
so naturally, there will
be some catering to fans.
She's right about that.
In fact, the game's attracted
quite a bit of attention.
‐You're kinda famous.
‐Cool!
Sounds like it'll be fun.
Looks like we're gonna have
to train like nobody's business
‐so we can kick some "A"!
‐[chuckles]
So, anyway. Thank you.
That was actually
pretty solid advice.
Of course. I suppose
it's the least I could do.
Okay, guys!
Time to nut up or shut up!
Let's do this thing
and start training!
Sorry, but it's too late
for training today.
What?
We have a press conference
tomorrow.
We have to be careful
we don't overdo it.
After all, it's important
that we look good
for the cameras.
Wait, when you say cameras‐‐
Yes, silly,
you're going to be on TV.
Try not to do anything stupid.
Hey, Gasper.
Do you think you're gonna wear
your girl's uniform
to the press conference later?
Uh, maybe?
It'd be strange to wear
a boy's uniform
after all this time.
Still though, I don't think
it'll make me less nervous!
[whimpers, screams]
I don't wanna go anymore!
I can't stand the thought
of everyone looking at me
‐during the stupid conference!
‐[KIBA and ISSEI laugh]
Huh?
Uh, Koneko? Can I get up?
Sounds like something
you should ask a doctor.
Unless we're not talking about
your junk, then the answer's no.
You seem rather feisty lately.
It seems Ravel's interest
in Issei
has made you
even more possessive.
Whoa, say what?
"Cunt‐tucky" Fried Chicken's
in love with you.
Jeez, get a clue, Mr. Nice Guy.
Uh‐oh, looks like some kitty's
a little green with envy.
‐That's so cute.
‐[groans]
She's right.
I guess Issei really is
Mr. Nice Guy... to everyone.
[ISSEI]
Hmm?
‐Huh?
‐[STAFF] Pardon me.
We are ready for you now.
What's up! Good to see you!
‐It's been a hot minute.
‐[RIAS] Hello, Saji.
‐Hey, bro.
‐Yo, how's it hangin'?
To the left.
What are you doing here?
Come on,
you seriously don't know?
Guess that's not a big surprise.
We actually have a rating game
the same day that you guys do.
And yet, no one seems
to really know about it.
Then again, we poke
a lot less boobs in our game.
That's probs a factor.
Anyway we got a press meeting.
Really? Shit!
How have I not heard about it?
Oh, right.
Did I forget to mention that?
Well, it's certainly news to me
[SAJI laughs]
Don't sweat it.
We haven't gotten
that much attention, really.
But hey, sounds like
the whole Underworld's psyched
‐about your game.
‐[chuckles nervously]
Hey, Saji, let's go.
Okay. See you losers later!
Totally. Take names
and all that jazz.
Will do. Good luck out there.
[indistinct chattering]
[MODERATOR]
Thank you for waiting.
And now, we are proud to welcome
the Gremory Family.
[people gasp]
[cameras clicking]
All right.
Both families are present,
so let's begin.
First, allow me to welcome
the Kings of each family.
Now, each King
will have the chance to comment
on the upcoming match.
Sairaorg will go first,
followed by Rias,
so please reserve
any comments for afterward.
Lord Bael? Please, start.
Yes, thank you.
Well, then...
I guess I'm just really excited
for this battle to begin.
I intend to fight
the Gremory family
with all my strength.
That's it for me.
I'm so honored to be fighting
against the Bael family
and look forward
to an interesting match.
Although he is considered
top‐ranking
among the younger devils,
I have no intention of losing.
In fact, I plan to win.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Next up. We will open the floor
for questions from the press.
Who's first?
[FEMALE REPORTER]
I have a question
for the biggest rising star
in the Underworld,
the Grabbin' Dragon,
Issei Hyodo.
‐Uh, 'kay.
‐So, do you intend to poke
Princess Rias' breasts
during the Rating Game?
Uh‐‐ uh, well, I‐‐
[FEMALE REPORTER] If you were
to poke them, when would it be?
And what about the reports?
Many say that,
like your stage show,
you're only able to power up
when you poke her boobs.
[nervous laugh]
And is it true
you've used this crude technique
to overcome
other dangerous situations?
Uh, when you say it like that‐‐
you know, it's sucky, but‐
[FEMALE REPORTER]
"Sucky Butt"?
What kind of sick code name
is that
for the princess's breasts?
[reporters shouting]
I have a question.
Do you happen to suck
‐her boobs, butt, or both?
‐[gasps]
[ISSEI] Holy hell, I just had
the worst word vomit ever!
I was trying to say
it was "sucky but necessary,"
and they didn't let me finish!
Does that indicate
that you'll be sucking
on her breasts
in the middle of the match?
[FEMALE REPORTER]
If you power up
when you poke them,
what happens
when you suck
those puppies instead?
Do you get even stronger?
Like, could you destroy
the Underworld with that power?
Please, Princess,
would you care to comment
on this matter at all?
[whimpers]
‐Nope. No comment.
‐[giggles]
And what are your thoughts
on this, Sairaorg?
[ISSEI]
Oh snap. Don't ask her cousin!
[silence]
Hmm. I suspect if he
were to suck Rias' breasts,
then the Red Dragon Emperor
would become even stronger.
[reporters gasp, murmur]
[ISSEI] Bro! Why'd you have
to teabag my rep like that?
‐[cameras clicking]
‐[MAN] Wow.
[SAIRAORG laughs]
Well, that was... something.
Am I right?
Never a dull moment with you,
huh?
That's what I like about
fighting the Grabbin' Dragon.
Yes, well, no one was talking
about your boobs
on public television.
Uh. I'm sorry.
I swear, we're taking
this Rating Game hella serious.
And I don't doubt it.
Honestly, I was pretty impressed
by the whole thing.
This may sound crazy,
but it takes some serious balls
to talk like that in front
of so many people.
I like that I never know
what to expect from you.
The next time you and I meet
will be in the arena.
‐Bring it.
‐[humphs]
You sound determined.
Well, then see you
in the sky, Red Dragon.
[humphs]
[water running]
[ISSEI sighs] That conference
was a total clusterfuck.
[groans]
I wonder if there's any way
I could say I was possessed?
[gasps]
Issei. What a surprise.
‐[door closes]
‐[grunts]
[ISSEI, strained]
Yeah. Come here often?
Well, nothing to see here!
[nervous chuckle]
Oh, come on now.
‐Stay a bit longer, would you?
‐[yelps]
If you insist!
[gasps]
‐It's just the two of us.
‐Uhh...
What a rarity,
since you're usually
surrounded by people.
You know, this steamy setting
is kind of romantic.
What if you took all of me
right here and now?
I realize after all this time
my body may be old news.
Is it possible it doesn't
do it for you anymore?
[gulps] Nope!
That's definitely not the case.
Trust me, I'm pitching
a serious tent right now!
[RIAS]
Okay.
So, do something about it.
I want you to give in
to your urges.
[whimpers]
Issei. What am I to you?
How do you think of me?
Uh, you mean
like besides the club president?
I get it. Then I'll show you
what else I can be.
[whimpering]
[gasps]
[ISSEI]
My brain, among other things,
feels like it's gonna explode!
[shudders] Oh my god,
it's finally happening!
I just got a one‐way ticket
to Pound Town!
Thanks, universe!
I'm gonna become a man!
Tonight, Issei.
I want all of you.
‐[moans]
‐[ISSEI] Ohh.
Wow, her milkshakes
are all up in my yard!
So much so, I can feel her
heart beating against my chest.
Note to self:
This is the new number‐one
moment for the ol' spank bank!
I am swapping spit
like a total champ right now.
I mean, who knew
watching so much porn
would make me
a badass in the sack?
‐[moans]
‐[ISSEI] I may not be a chef,
but I'm about to stuff me
this turkey!
Holy shit, my first time's
gonna be in a sauna,
which is so friggin' hot!
Literally and figuratively!
[both moan, pant]
Oh. You're amazing, President!
[gasps]
President?
We're about to make
passionate love,
and you want to call me...
a title?
I can't believe that.
How could you?
President? Are you okay?
‐Enough, Issei!
‐[gasps]
Huh?
[sighs]
What's up, Gasper? How're things
going between Koneko and Ravel?
Well....
Fine, except for the whole
"fighting like cats
and chickens" thing.
Sounds about right.
But even though she kinda
complains the whole time,
I've noticed that Koneko
still helps Ravel out,
and while she usually has
a comeback ready,
Ravel does at least seem willing
to listen
to Koneko's instructions.
If you ask me,
it sounds like we can
probably count that as a win.
[groans] Why do girls
always have to be so confusing?
To be fair,
jealousy can bring out the worst
in just about anyone.
That's why they can't help
butting heads like that.
Azazel?
Uh, I don't really get
what you mean.
[AZAZEL chuckles]
I wish I could be helpful
to Ravel
in the same way Koneko is,
but I can't even support
someone in battle.
I don't know where I'd start
if I had to help somebody
like that.
I'm the most useless
person ever.
[ISSEI]
Gasper.
Listen up, I'm about
to drop some knowledge on ya.
Rule number one for any boys
in the Gremory household:
A real man always protects
the ladies, got it?
‐Yeah.
‐Now repeat it back.
Oh, um, a real man
always protects the ladies.
Rule two:
A real man stands up tall
‐regardless of the situation!
‐Right.
A real man stands up tall
regardless of the situation!
Last one!
No matter what happens,
never, ever, give up!
don't give up, ever!
Good! You nailed it.
If you ever get scared
or unsure,
just remember you're a man
of the Gremory family.
I've got it now! Right!
I promise to do my best!
Sounds good in theory,
but let's see how it goes, yes?
Start with baby steps.
Uh... [sighs]
[AZAZEL] All right.
Let's get started, shall we?
[clears throat]
First up. I have
a bit of news for everybody.
As it turns out, I've been
appointed as your advisor
for the upcoming Rating Game
with Sairaorg.
Hold up. If you're our advisor,
does Sairaorg also have
some know‐it‐all
that's gonna do crap for him?
Of course.
He will have the emperor
to act as his advisor.
His name is Diehauser Belial.
Wait, as in the Rating Game
champion or whatever?
[KIBA]
Yes. He's quite accomplished.
He's the long‐standing champion
of the Rating Game
as well as the head
of the Belial clan.
Don't freak out.
You guys have me. Lucky ducks.
Now, on to the next order
of business.
[hums]
I trust you all had a chance
to memorize the data I gave you?
These are the members
of Sairaorg's family.
Like you, they're also
rare types of devils,
and they constantly train.
Well, if that's the case,
then the chances are pretty good
they'll be even more powerful
at the game than they are now.
Yes, I think
we can count on that.
But what about their pawns?
As I recall,
they've never appeared
in a recorded battle before.
Now that I think about it,
I don't remember seeing any
at the press conference, either.
That's correct.
And we have little to no
information on them.
Whoever they are,
it's likely they're Sairaorg's
hidden trump card.
Okay then. Moving on,
Rias is going
to go over our battle tactics
and countermeasures
for the match in detail.
Thank you.
Please look at the screen.
As you can see
from the above image,
Sairaorg's team has one queen,
as well as two rooks.
With that,
why don't we call it a day?
One more thing, though.
If you were to join
the professional league,
you'd definitely climb
the ranks.
You already have
enough power for success.
‐That's nothing to scoff at.
‐[grumbles]
So, be proud, and take this
challenge on with confidence.
[GROUP]
Yes, sir!
[XENOVIA]
Hey, Asia, is this right?
[GASPER] It's so cute!
Don't you think so?
[KONEKO]
Fo sho, I couldn't agree more.
[XENOVIA] Thanks.
Akeno, see if we can't find any
more info on this one, please.
‐[humming]
‐[both gasp]
‐Good afternoon, Ravel, dear.
‐[RAVEL] Mother!
‐[MOTHER] Are Rias and
the Red Dragon Emperor available
by any chance?
Why, hello there, Auntie.
It's been quite a while.
Indeed, it has been, Rias.
Good to see you. You look well.
Hi. I'm Issei Hyodo.
Nice to meet ya.
So, you're the Dragon Emperor.
It's so nice to meet you
as well.
I've heard many
wonderful things about you,
and I feel so rude that I can't
be there to meet you in person.
Oh, no, you good! But there
was something you needed me for?
[MOTHER] Well, yes,
it's nothing too important.
I just wanted
to introduce myself,
even if it's not
in a more proper manner.
Seriously, Auntie,
please stop worrying about it.
We're happy to see you
however we can.
Thank you, Rias.
I did want to ask Mister Hyodo
to take good care of my daughter
while she's
attending your school.
Uh, yeah, totally.
I'll be a real boss about it,
and thankfully
the president's here too,
and she can def keep
a better eye on your girl.
[MOTHER] Of course.
Naturally, that's reassuring.
However,
I'm asking that you protect
from the various evils
of the human world specifically.
The evils
of the whatty‐what now?
If the Red Dragon Emperor,
who's famous
for his numerous,
distinguished victories
stays by my Ravel's side,
then I know my husband and I
will be able to feel more
at ease
while she's away from home,
and we can hope for good news.
Yeah, I hear ya loud and clear,
Missus Phoenix, ma'am.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of your daughter!
‐[gasps]
‐[MOTHER] Thank you so much.
And as for you, Ravel dear,
be on your best behavior,
all right?
Make sure you always listen
to Rias and follow her example.
Study hard to learn as much
as you can about the human world
and make our family proud.
Of course, Mother!
And as a personal favor to me,
try to be good friends
with the Dragon Emperor.
‐One more thing.
‐Uh, what's up?
Rumor has it that you wish
to become a high‐ranking devil.
That's right. Um. Why?
It just so happens
that my daughter
has been returned to my family.
I conducted a trade with Riser
for her.
As such, there's something
I wanted to let you know.
Right now, she's available.
Keep that in mind.
‐Yes ma'am. I gotcha!
‐[gasps]
Thank you, what a relief!
Well then. Good day, everyone!
[RIAS scoffs]
Uh, hey. Something wrong, Prez?
Issei. I need to know.
Will you protect me?
Yeah, of course.
I'd die for you, President.
‐[RIAS] What about Asia?
‐[ISSEI] Huh?
Yeah, I'd protect her, too.
[RIAS]
And Akeno?
[ISSEI chuckles]
Duh, totally! Why wouldn't I?
Still though.
Why are you asking?
Somethin' up?
‐Issei. Tell me.
‐Yeah, what?
What am I to you?
How do you see me?
Umm...
Just answer me, already!
Okay, uh. Let me think.
‐Well, you're the president.
‐[sobs]
You're an ass!
‐Uhh...
‐Oh, god.
[ASIA]
Rias, wait!
I can't believe you, Issei!
[ISSEI]
Huh?
‐But...
‐[KIBA] Even by your standards,
‐that was way oblivious.
‐Huh?
I don't get it. What'd I do?
Man, I don't know
where to begin.
And honestly, no one should have
to explain it to you
at this point.
Why is it everyone in this room
knows exactly what you
did wrong, except you?
Yeah, sorry, but you are, like,
seriously
the dumbest guy ever, Issei.
You can suck it.
‐Don't you dare.
‐Huh?
If you go after her right now
without knowing
why you're going,
you'll only make things worse.
What about you, Gasper?
Do you think I'm a piece
of shit, too?
Well, yeah. I actually kinda do.
[gasps, sighs]
I'm sorry.
This all happened
because of my mother and I,
didn't it?
No, of course not, sweetie.
no one blames you.
If anything,
it's obviously Issei's fault
for being such
an incredibly brainless dildo
when it comes to
Rias's feelings.
[gasps]
What's a brainless dildo to do?
[ISSEI] "The Deciding Battle
of the Strongest Youth Begins!"