[KIDS cheering, shouting]
Oh no, kids! The Grabbin'
Dragon's in a real pinch!
We have to say the magic words
to send him our strength!
All together.
[KIDS]
Yay, boobies!
[ISSEI shouts]
I refuse to fall here!
Thankfully, the audience's power
has made me even stronger!
[KIBA laughs] Give it up
already, you handsy pansy!
‐[ISSEI] Low blow!
‐You can't defeat me,
for I am
the Darkness Knight Fang!
[flatly]
Help. Someone save me.
Like a hero.
No, better, the Grabbin' Dragon.
[sighs]
[ISSEI]
One day, not too long
before the school festival
or whatever,
everyone in the Gremory family
was asked
to put on a kid's show
for the Underworld.
Curse you, fiend!
‐[both grunt]
‐[KIBA laughs]
[shouts]
‐Huh?
‐[air hisses]
Have you had enough yet?
This show's pretty good!
Yeah, and the acting
is on point!
Personally, I like the special
effects and wire work action.
And it looks like
they did a lot of research
on kids' shows
in the human world to prepare.
[KIBA]
It's over, Grabbin' Dragon!
[ISSEI] Curses! If only
the Princess were by side,
then I could power up!
‐[gasps]
‐[MAN] Grabbin' Dragon,
now is the time
for your special move!
[ISSEI]
Of course. Let's go!
Summon, Tig Ole Bitties!
‐[gasps] It's the Princess!
‐[kids cheering]
Please. Forgive me.
Here we go, kids!
Say it with me!
Boop, boop, go!
[KIDS]
It worked!
Now I have all the power I need!
That's enough of your nonsense!
‐[shouts]
‐[ISSEI] Dragon Kick!
[shouts]
[explosion]
The Grabbin' Dragon
has won the battle,
and it's all thanks
to our lovely audience!
[KIDS cheering]
[BOTH chuckle]
‐[NARRATOR]
But wait! Who's that?
‐[RIAS] Huh?
‐[NARRATOR] Up on that pillar!
Is it a bird? Is it a plane?
No, it's Little Hellcat!
Meow.
[GUYS]
Little Hellcat!
[cheering, shouting]
[yelps, grunts]
[KIBA] Man, the crowd
really loves you, Issei.
Nah, only the really
little kids cheered for me.
But all the fine ass mamacitas
in the crowd
were totally creaming their
pants when you got up on stage.
Seriously, not a dry seat
in the house.
[KIBA sighs] Well, I've got
to give it to Sir Zechs.
This whole thing
has gotten really popular.
‐[knock on door]
‐[BOTH] Huh?
[ISSEI]
Irina. What's up?
Don't ask questions.
Just come with me!
[ISSEI grunting]
Tell me again why we're
squeezing you into this dress?
The usual lady narrator person
twisted her ankle or something,
so they asked
if maybe I could fill in.
‐[ISSEI] Hold up, that's right.
‐Yeah! Show him who's boss,
‐Grabbin Dragon! You can do it!
‐[ISSEI] I think you were
more excited about the show
than any of the kids.
I don't mind filling in for her,
but the costume is
a little tight.
Especially around the chest
area, you know?
I gotcha.
Okay, suck everything in!
‐[grunts]
‐[rips]
[BOTH yelp]
[grunts]
That hurt.
[gasps] Hold on!
Why are you going commando?
Well, I thought the suit
would fit better without a bra.
Wait a second, random side note.
What?
We've been
in this position before.
Uh, not this exact one!
Okay, then. I get it.
Things like this
always happen with you.
It must be a sign from God!
We'll be like the animals
on the ark!
Minus the flood
and boat thing, right?
No, but there's a sizable canoe
in your pocket!
If I have
the Red Dragon Emperor's child,
it'll prove
my faithfulness to God.
I know he'll forgive me!
[ISSEI]
Holy angel tits!
‐[whimpering]
‐Oh, God!
This is for you!
Take me, Issei!
Stop right there!
I have dibs on that DNA!
No fair, you can't
take advantage of Issei!
Especially since that's my job.
Move aside, douche‐hoes,
because that man is mine.
Hey, back off! I was here first!
Ignore those milk troughs.
I'm built for speed!
Oh please. You mean
you're built like a boy.
‐Pick me!
‐Well, mine are the perfect size
for baby making.
Get out of the way!
‐[clamoring]
‐[RIAS] What is going on?
[ISSEI]
Uh... wrestling?
You girls have exactly five
seconds to clear this room!
[GIRLS scream]
[RIAS]
I swear.
Whew. Crazy.
I guess actors really do
get all the chicks.
[BOY] No fair! You said
we were gonna get to meet him!
I wanna see the Grabbin Dragon!
You promised!
‐[crying]
‐I'm so sorry.
I'm afraid we've already
sold out of the meet‐n‐greet
and autograph spots
for this evening.
How unfortunate. Looks like
they're out of tickets, honey.
We'll have to try again
on another day.
No fair!
But I wanna see him today!
‐You promised me!
‐[ISSEI] What's going on?
[gasps]
[laughs]
It's the Grabbin' Dragon!
‐You're so cool!
‐Mr. Hyodo, I'm sorry.
‐What's your name, buddy?
‐It's Lirenkus!
Ah, cool name, bro!
I'm psyched that you and your
mom came out to see me today.
Listen, real men
don't throw fits, okay?
You gotta be super strong
and protect your mom.
‐[LIRENKUS] 'Kay!
‐[ISSEI] Here.
[laughs] Awesome!
Thanks,
Mr. Grabbin' Dragon, sir!
See ya later!
And thanks again for everything!
Mr. Hyodo, please don't do
spontaneous things
like that in the future.
It's simply impossible
to accommodate
every single child
who comes through here.
And quite frankly,
it sets a bad precedent.
Uh, yeah, I guess you're right.
[RIAS]
You never cease to amaze me.
President! Uh, how much
of that did you see?
Just enough to be impressed.
Nah. I mean it's not like
it was anything special.
Hm‐mmm. On the contrary,
I think it was special to him.
Really?
‐[MILLICAS] Hi, Issei!
‐[door closes]
[MILLICAS] I saw your show!
It was super amazing!
Mother, Millicas.
How nice to see you.
We enjoyed the hero
show very much.
[ISSEI]
Wow, thanks a lot!
We never anticipated
that it would be so popular,
but thanks to its success,
we'll be able to keep funding
the Gremory family's
future endeavors.
The children of the Underworld
are smitten with it.
They simply can't get enough
of the Grabbin' Dragon.
I hope that you'll continue
the wonderful work
you're doing here,
not only for all the children
of the Underworld,
but for the rest of the
Gremory family
and our beloved
daughter as well.
Oh, yes, ma'am!
I won't let you down!
Don't you worry
Miss President's Mom!
[VENERANA] Thank you, though
I'd really prefer you call me
something else besides
"Miss President's Mom".
You could always call me
"Mother‐in‐law"
or, better yet, just "Mother."
I dunno, sounds kinda kinky.
No, it's only kinky
if you say "Mommy."
Besides, it's embarrassing
for you to be so formal with me,
especially during public events.
And furthermore,
I'm not sure why
you've taken to calling Rias
"President" in the first place.
‐[ISSEI] Huh?
‐Tell me, Issei,
‐do you love my daughter?
‐Duh!
Of course I do!
I love her, and respect her,
and all that other stuff dudes
say to get lucky!
I would rather die than let
anything bad happen to her!
I see.
That confirms your beautiful
master‐and‐servant relationship.
And those feelings
are quite natural,
but what about
beyond that?
As in, what does Rias
mean to you personally,
not only as your master,
but as something more?
Yeah, good question.
Uh, I'll think on it.
Rias. It's not just Issei. You
should think about it, as well.
[RIAS]
Right.
[door opens, closes]
[RIAS] Well, we should
probably head home
and start prepping
for the school festival.
'Cause... there's still a lot
that needs to be sorted out.
Okay.
[STUDENT 7A] So, tell us
all about where you're from!
[STUDENT 7B] Phoenix is such a
cool last name!
It sounds like a superhero!
[STUDENT 7C] This class is big
on overseas transfer students,
like not that long ago we got
this total cutie named Gasper.
[STUDENT 7D] Ooh, maybe we could
grab some tea together sometime!
Sounds delightful.
[nervous laugh]
[RIAS] I wanted to
check in on Ravel
since she just transferred here.
Is it me or does she seem
a little nervous?
[ISSEI]
Yeah. Which is like hella weird.
I thought she'd be all like...
[loud laugh]
Ask me your questions, mortals,
and I shall answer you!
She's so normal.
‐[STUDENTS gasp]
‐Uh, please excuse me.
[ISSEI grunts]
‐[sighs]
‐Is something wrong?
Well, this is the first time
I've ever transferred schools,
and seeing as I'm a devil
and all that,
I have no idea how
I'm supposed to interact
with these overly‐curious
human teenagers.
Sucks to be you right now.
I can see how that might be
a little nerve‐wracking for you,
so perhaps
we could find a classmate
that you'd be
more familiar with.
Yo, what it do?
We have a favor to ask. I'm sure
you remember Ravel Phoenix.
We were hoping
you could be her friend
and explain
how things work here.
Sure, whatevs.
Besides, cats love
fried chicken.
Did you just call me a chicken?
‐Yeah. So?
‐[scoffs] How dare you!
I can't believe
you have the audacity
to insult a member
of the Phoenix family!
You've only been
at this school for one day
and you're already
causing a bunch
of problems
for the prez and Issei,
so all things considered,
you're lucky I stopped
at "fried chicken."
Well, better a fried chicken
than a little pussy!
‐Wish granted.
‐[growls]
[whimpers]
But she's so scary!
Come on.
It's not like she's a monster,
so you could at least try
and get along.
When did you get
into friendship mediating?
‐What are you talking about?
‐[scofffs]
Uh, I'm just trying to be
a good example
to the younger students!
Why do you gotta bust
my chops about it?
[RAVEL and KONEKO growl]
I'm worried that our super
awesome plan wasn't so awesome.
Yes. I'm concerned, too.
All right then.
Everyone know what to do now?
[ALL]
Yeah!
[AKENO] We get to make
the old school building
into an occult mansion.
Talk about exciting!
[XENOVIA] There's gonna be a
haunted house,
and a fortune teller,
oh, and a maid café, too!
Should be a lot of fun, huh?
I'm excited too,
but I'm a little worried
about taking
on such a large project
when we don't have
that much time
to complete everything
in the first place.
It's not like we haven't pulled
off impossible feats before.
I believe in us!
[KIBA] Hey, Issei,
have you given any thought
to the Rating Game
with Sairaorg?
[ISSEI]
Yeah. I'm trying to figure out
how I can beat that guy.
[KIBA] The dude's tough.
Sairaorg does know
some of our basic moves,
and we know about his,
but we can surprise him
with stuff like your new skill
and Xenovia's Ex‐Durandal.
The game's outcome may depend
on how we play those new assets.
[ISSEI] The combo attack
saps my power like a mofo,
so I gotta be sure to save
that kick‐ass technique
for just the right moment.
I'll train with you,
if you want to.
I've been working
on the framework
for a brand‐new attack.
‐[ISSEI] You too, huh?
‐It's a secret, though.
[AZAZEL] Looks like
some intense male bonding.
[chuckles]
What's with the whispering?
Oh, you know, just wondering
if someone pissed
in your hair or what.
Anyway, didn't you have
a staff meeting?
Meh, it was boring,
so I ditched it and left
Rossweisse there to take notes.
Jerk move.
I'm actually here
to speak to Ddraig
about a personal matter.
I found the name
of that counselor.
[DDRAIG]
Thanks, sorry for the trouble.
Why does he need to talk
to a counselor?
Ever since the Kyoto trip he's
had sudden bouts of depression,
so he used Fafnir's orb
to ask if I could help find him
a counselor for his issues.
Words like "fun bags"
or "jubblies" are
a trigger for him.
The poor guy just spirals
into a dark place.
[gasps]
Seriously, bro?
[DDRAIG] Yes,
I can't seem to get over it,
but don't worry about me.
Regardless of how I feel,
you should be able
to power up when needed.
Yup. It looks like boob miracles
are pretty hard on him.
I mean, not everyone
is as perverted as you are.
Ddraig is a heavenly dragon
after all.
He's supposed to be a creature
full of dignity and honor.
I mean, using pillows
to power up?
Well, it's no surprise
it makes the guy upset.
Yeah, I guess I never really
thought of it like that before.
You know, now that you've
mentioned it, Ddraig does seem
to cry anytime I use Rias' nips
to get super swole or whatever.
[DDRAIG] I'm sorry,
it seems my spirit
isn't as strong
as I thought it was.
[emotionally]
I am ashamed!
Hey, you shouldn't
have to apologize
just 'cause your dude's
a total boob‐loving man‐whore
who relies on a girl's nips
to power up! I'm sorry!
[AZAZEL]
Well, it was no easy feat,
finding a counselor
that specialized in dragons.
I'll shoot
over the contact info.
I'm a total failure
as a partner.
[DDRAIG cries]
Don't say that.
[ISSEI] Can you forgive me?
Even though there will
constantly be hooters around me,
I'll always care
about you more, probably!
[DDRAIG]
Ah. Well, at this point
I suppose I'll take
what I can get.
[crying]
Just do your best.
[emotionally]
Okay, I'll try.
Just hang in there, good buddy!
[sobbing]
[RIAS] Sorry to interrupt
you and your hand.
Huh? President!
We need to talk about something
that's been worrying me.
I got a call
from Sairaorg's butler.
He would like to request
a personal favor
from the two of us, so...
Whoa, he has his own butler?
I've never actually been
to the Sitri domain before.
Guess it's no surprise
it's so nice.
Indeed. Besides being pretty,
it's also one of the few domains
with exceptional
medical facilities.
That's hella dope.
Anyway, the place we're
going to now
is one of the best there is.
Initially, Sairaorg's butler
contacted my mother
before he reached out to me.
Remind me, did I ever tell you
that my mother is
from the Bael family?
Maybe? No, wait, I think
you have mentioned it,
and that's where the whole
cousin thing comes into play?
Yes, that's correct, but what
I probably failed to tell you is
that his mother is
from the Vapula family,
AKA one of the 72 pillars.
They carry
the symbol of the lion.
That sounds pretty bad ass,
and it's fitting, for Sairaorg.
‐[heart monitor beeping]
‐May I present Lady Misla Bael.
She is Lord Sairaorg's
beloved mother.
Thank you both for coming all
this way on such short notice.
Lord Sairaorg does not know
that I have asked you here,
but I beg you to hear me out.
Please, Lady Rias,
Red Dragon Emperor,
do you think you could possibly
lend us your strength
and help us to awaken
Lady Misla from her slumber?
Uh, yeah, I don't really follow.
Right, I'll try
to explain, then.
See, when Sairaorg was born
into the Bael family,
everyone was overjoyed
to hear the news
that an heir
had finally been born.
However, shortly afterwards,
his birth proved to be
a disappointment to his family.
Let me guess, it's because he
didn't have any demonic power?
Mm‐hmm.
Not only that,
it was also very upsetting
that the new child
hadn't inherited the family's
emblematic Power of Destruction.
Sairaorg's father felt such
dishonor that he blamed
his own wife for the disgrace
of their "defective son."
After that, she had
no choice but to live
the rest of her life
in the shadows.
[ISSEI]
That blows.
My mother tried
to take the two of them in,
but Lord Bael refused her.
They are a very proud family,
and that pride made it
to where he saw them
as an embarrassment.
It's silly, really,
but he didn't want anyone
to find out about them.
[BUTLER] Lady Misla was forced
to raise Lord Sairaorg
in the outlands
of the Bael domain.
They had very little choice
in the matter.
When Lord Sairaorg was a child,
he would cry frequently,
but the lady would tell him...
Don't cry, at least you
still have a strong body.
Why don't you make it
even stronger,
so you can make up
for what you don't have?
You may not have demonic power,
but you are still
a child of Bael.
"You will definitely win as
long as you never give up hope."
Those are the words
she used to say to him.
They meant a lot to Sairaorg,
and he's always treasured them.
[BUTLER]
However, she was still concerned
for him deep in her heart.
She used to shed so many tears,
worrying over her son.
Sometimes she would sit
by his bedside and just cry.
Lady Misla's feelings must
have reached him, though,
because Lord Sairaorg grew up
to be a strong
and resilient young master.
But, just as the rays of hope
had finally deigned
to shine on Lord Sairaorg,
the poor Lady Misla
unexpectedly fell
into a demonic sickness.
It's a very rare disease here
in the underworld
that only affects devils.
Once the illness takes hold,
the victim falls
into a deep, unending sleep.
Their bodies eventually
grow weak and perish.
At this moment, they're doing
all they can to keep her alive.
[ISSEI] That sucks, but why do
you think I'll be able to help?
I'm no doctor.
Well, I heard that you possess
a rather unique power,
one that enables you to listen
to the inner thoughts
of a woman's bosom?
[gasps]
Boobielingual?
Please, Red Dragon Emperor,
use your special ability
to listen to Lady Misla's voice!
Her doctor already approved
of your involvement.
‐I'm begging you, sir.
‐I don't know.
At least consider it, Issei.
Your power has been able
to do so many amazing things
in the past.
Think about this.
You might be it,
the only person
who has the ability to reach
‐my aunt's consciousness.
‐Okay, I'll try.
[breathes hard]
[ISSEI] I'm really sorry.
I let you down.
[RIAS]
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Sure, we weren't able
to hear her voice,
but it's not like
you didn't try your best.
[ISSEI]
Still.
You even used
your Balance Break.
You increased your power
to its absolute highest limit,
and did everything
you possibly could.
I'm sure her butler was
thankful for what you did.
[sighs]
[SAIRAORG]
Hey there.
‐[ISSEI] Sairaorg!
‐I heard what you did.
Thank you, both.
I appreciate it.
Dude, you don't have
to thank us.
We didn't do jack, seriously.
[RIAS]
Yes, if anything,
I should probably
be apologizing to you,
especially since I told
Issei about your past...
right before
our Rating Game, no less.
[SAIRAORG]
Forget about it.
[scoffs]
It's the worst‐kept secret
among high‐ranking
devil families.
Unless‐‐ you're not thinking
about going easy on me
during our game out of pity
or anything, are you, Issei?
‐Hmm?
‐Uh, wasn't planning on it.
[SAIRAORG]
Excellent.
In the end,
my past doesn't matter.
All I want is to have
a good ol' fashioned brawl
with the Gremory family.
This is all I've got.
For someone who has nothing,
the only path
is the one of victory.
If I lose even once, I risk
losing everything else.
The only power I can rely on
is my own body.
And that's why
I'm going to come at you
with everything I have.
Yeah, the past is in the past,
and it won't keep me
from kicking yo ass!
Your soap opera childhood
isn't enough
to make me let up,
got that?
Maybe it sounds crazy,
but I have a dream
about becoming
a high‐ranking devil one day!
I'm gonna do whatever it takes.
But in order for that to happen,
I gotta defeat you in
the upcoming Rating Game.
It's not personal or anything,
so try to remember that when
I'm kicking your teeth in!
Yes, now that's
the kinda fiery passion
you can cook a s'more on.
It seems you've not
only gained strength,
but also confidence
since our last encounter.
[ISSEI] Huh?
The rating game will be
an event to remember,
and I'm looking forward
to facing you both
on the battlefield soon.
We're looking
forward to it, too.
[chuckles]
[RIAS]
Issei looks so strong right now.
Maybe that's the reason I‐‐
Yes, that's why.
Hm. Hey, are you okay?
[chuckles]
[ISSEI whines]
"A Girl's Heart is Complicated."