[moans]
[AKENO]
Issei, I want you.
Akeno? Um...
[whimpers]
[AKENO] I can't believe
you'd abandon me
just so you can go
gallivanting all over Kyoto.
Come on! It wasn't my idea.
I'm going for
a school trip, you know?
I do,
but that's two entire days
I won't be able
to get my hands on you.
Really.
And so, that's why I'm going
to fill up on you now.
Fill what up?
[AKENO]
You're so funny.
I meant I want to experience
your manly essence.
And in turn, I want to feel
your hands all over me.
Yeah, that sounds amazing,
but we shouldn't
since you're a senior.
There's no such thing as seniors
or juniors in the boudoir.
There's only a man and a woman.
[gasps] I happen to be a man.
‐[RIAS] Akeno?
‐[AKENO gasps]
[RIAS] What the hell
is going on in here?
[AKENO]
Oh my, what's this?
It looks as though our bicycle
is in danger
of becoming a tricycle.
‐[AKENO giggles]
‐[ISSEI] President!
You seem to be having a hard
time controlling yourself.
I'm not the only one having
a hard time right now.
Right?
‐[AKENO giggles]
‐[ISSEI gasps]
Yo, stop hogging
all the man meat.
Hold up, when did you get here?
Issei, let's use
my healing sage arts
to get you back
to full capacity.
[ISSEI]
Huh?
Wow. You, too?
[ASIA]
Oh, no!
It looks like once again
I'm the odd woman out.
Well, no more!
‐I want in!
‐[ISSEI grunts]
[ASIA] Tonight, I'm gonna be
the one to sleep with Issei
if it's the last thing I do!
[AKENO] As if, I've already
called dibs on him!
His healing comes first.
[ISSEI thinking]
I've heard of using pillows
to smother
someone before,
but this‐‐ this is the kind of
pillow‐death I can get behind!
Jeez. Why can't
any of you subs
learn to listen
to your master's orders?
[ALL]
Because Issei is ours.
[chuckles]
No!
If anything,
he belongs to me!
‐[ISSEI gasping]
‐[RIAS yelling]
[theme music playing]
[KIRYUU]
It looks like we'll have to do
most of the sightseeing
on the second day.
So what do you guys wanna see?
Kiyomizu Temple.
Oh, what about that
shiny golden temple place?
Oh! You mean Kinkakuji.
I remember 'cause
it sounds like "kinky."
[MATSUDA] Yo, I'm psyched
we're gonna be touring it up
with the hottest shorties
in our class.
Of course, that's only
if you don't count
that fugly she‐perv, Kiryuu.
Kinda pisses me off
that it's all 'cause
of this bro right here.
[ISSEI] Thanks for
the sort‐of‐compliment,
but here's a newsflash
for you:
Even if our tour groups
are the same
we're still in totally
separate hotel rooms.
Oh please, as if
we weren't aware!
Check out the booby backlog
that I've been
saving for this trip!
[MATSUDA chuckles]
For real?!
Hey, lame brains.
Unfortunately, we need
your opinions, too.
Lay off woman, we got serious
dude business to take care of.
[KIRYUU] Ew,
is that what you call it?
[MATSUDA]
You ain't got no business...
[KONEKO] Can I borrow you
for a minute, perv?
You wanna heal me and junk?
In here?
Yes.
I need to treat you as much
as I can before you leave.
The only way to recover
the life force you lost
from using
the Juggernaut Drive
is through regular
sage arts healing sessions,
and I'm worried
we'll lose progress
with you being gone
for two whole days.
[ISSEI] I guess
that makes sense, but...
There are too many
people at your house,
so it can be rather
difficult for me
to focus on
healing you properly.
We'll have to do it here.
[gasps]
Akeno kindly let me
borrow some of her clothes.
They help me
send my focused chi
to you more effectively.
[whimpers]
[ISSEI excited]
My body is ready!
[KONEKO] How does it feel?
Is it helping?
[ISSEI]
Yeah. It feels awesome.
There's another thing
we can try as well.
Um...
it's called Bedroom Arts.
Hold up, can you please
define "bedroom arts."
Like bumpin' uglies
for your health?
You really wanna do that
with me, Koneko?
You can't tell me a perv
like you wouldn't be interested.
It would help you recover.
If you say so.
‐[WOMAN clears throat]
‐[ISSEI gasps]
[ISSEI]
President?
While I understand the sage arts
are a necessary evil
needed to heal Issei,
I'll have to ask you to refrain
from doing the deed
on school grounds.
Also, I wanted to tell you
that my family
is having a gathering.
We'll be stopping by
the Gremory house to say hello.
Since you're leaving
for Kyoto shortly,
we'll go before your trip.
I never thought an angel
would visit the mansion
of an upper‐class devil.
I am beyond honored!
[VENERANA] Well,
the pleasure is all ours, dear.
[LORD GREMORY]
So, Rossweisse,
you're interested in
our educational system?
Yes! In fact, I was hoping
to open a Norse magic school
in the Gremory domain
in the near future.
I do think it'd be
very interesting
to try and raise
a few Valkyrie devils.
[LORD GREMORY laughs]
[LORD GREMORY] As head
of the Gremory household,
that sounds like a
fascinating endeavor.
Speaking of school,
doesn't your class
have a trip
coming up soon, Issei?
Yep! We're all hitting up Kyoto.
[VENERANA] Of course, Rias went
on that same trip last year.
She brought us back
some pickled vegetables
that were simply divine.
[ISSEI] I could score you
some veggies!
[VENERANA]
I was just making conversation,
but that's a sweet offer.
Though I hear their
melon balls are amazing.
[ISSEI chuckles]
[gasps]
[clears throat]
[LORD GREMORY]
Oh, yes. Did I mention
Sir Zechs is in
the residential suite?
[RIAS]
My brother's here?
Hey, Zechs.
How'd you know?
[RIAS]
Father told us.
How are you?
I hope well.
So good to see you.
There was no need to go
out of your way to see me,
but thanks.
This is a nice surprise!
If it isn't the
Ruin Princess herself
and the Red Dragon.
[RIAS]
Sairaorg!
I wish you would have told me
you were stopping
in for a visit.
[SIR ZECHS]
Good news is
he was kind enough
to bring along
some of that famous fruit
from the Bael domain.
Also, we used this opportunity
to discuss the details
of the Rating Game
you and he
will be participating in.
Outside of the usual
field rule requirements,
Sairaorg has also
requested to remove
any complicated rules of battle
within the Rating Game.
So basically, what
you're saying is that
you're going to allow all
of our various powers in combat?
Yeah, that's exactly
what I'm wanting.
If I can't take your people on
at full strength,
then I have
no business claiming
to be the heir
of a great devil family.
Indeed.
Sairaorg, weren't you
hoping to exchange
‐a few blows with Issei?
‐Yes.
Perfect, then why don't we
set up a quick bout right now?
[gasps] Like right now,
right now?
[SIR ZECHS]
What are your thoughts, Rias?
Fine by me.
I mean, if the Great Devil
wishes for it,
then, guess
I can't really refuse.
Issei, think you can handle it?
Uh, yeah, I'm pretty sure.
Most excellent.
I'm looking forward to seeing
what kind of power
the Red Dragon Emperor
possesses.
Aren't you, Sairaorg?
[SAIRAORG]
I've been looking forward
to this day for a while now.
[SIR ZECHS]
Now, begin the match!
[SAIRAORG snickers]
‐Let's kick ass, Ddraig.
‐[DDRAIG] Leave it to me!
One, two, three!
[SAIRAORG]
This should be interesting.
Hmmph.
[DDRAIG]
Welsh Dragon. Balance Breaker!
[ISSEI thinking]
Damn! He's too fast!
Guess I'll have to go
with a suicidal charge!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT yells]
Not bad, Issei.
That was a decent attack,
though maybe a little
too straightforward.
[gasps]
That move might
take down a weaker devil,
but I'm...
stronger!
[yells]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
What the hell?
That was my favorite
free‐time arm.
It's numb,
but I don't think it's broken.
Ddraig, can you
repair the armor?
[DDRAIG]
Yes. I'm on it.
[SAIRAORG]
Oh, you're still standing?
No matter, I'm just
getting warmed up.
[ISSEI thinking]
Warmed up?
You almost broke
Palmela Handerson, you bastard!
Let's go!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Oh, shit!
[grunts]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
He barely grazed me, but still.
Damn you!
[gasps]
‐[SAIRAORG grunts]
‐[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT exclaims]
[explosion]
[rumbling]
[ISSEI thinking]
What a beast!
Is this guy really
in the same generation
as the prez
and Diodora Astaroth?
[DDRAIG]
Yes. Even I'm surprised.
A power‐type that's
raised his physical strength
to its utmost
destructive limit?
How interesting!
I'll admit he's peaked
my curiosity.
[ISSEI thinking]
He should've inherited
the Power of Destruction,
but instead he was born into
a devil household without it.
The only thing he had
was his own body.
He became so strong on his own
that he was chosen
as the next heir.
This guy doesn't
half‐ass anything.
He's coming!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT grunts]
[groans]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Damn, dude!
How are you doing all this?
You on some kinda
'roid juice cleanse?
You don't need drugs when
you believe in your own body.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT] How the hell
did he make that sound cool?
Oh, well,
I won't give up either.
That's right!
I need to follow
Lord Beelzebub's advice.
Promotion to Rook!
[energy charging]
[DDRAIG echoing]
Boost!
[SAIRAORG grunts]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT coughs]
[gasping]
[ISSEI thinking]
It's just like I thought.
The defensive power of the Rook
helped me survive the attack.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Take this!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT yells]
[explosion]
[shattering]
[grunting]
[coughs]
[ISSEI thinking]
I'm not dead!
And my armor,
it's still intact!
I can do this.
I can beat Sairaorg!
Sure, I took
a shit ton of damage,
but I got a pretty good
hit in, too!
As long as I'm standing
this fight isn't over!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT pants]
You know, I packed quite a bit
of energy into that last punch.
[chuckles] But your attack
and defense power as a rook
are rather impressive.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Oh. Thanks, I guess.
Hmm, what's wrong?
You seem confused
by my compliment.
Do you have a problem with me?
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
No!
It's the opposite.
I'm just used
to upper‐class devils
looking down on me,
that's all.
[SAIRAORG]
Hmm. I get it now,
but honestly I could never
look down on the person
who went against
the old Satan faction
and the Northern God Loki.
All without dying, no less.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Sairaorg.
[chuckles]
Fighting with you
has been a lot of fun,
and when you fight someone
who's similar to yourself,
that's how you grow
as a warrior.
Now, come on!
Show me what
you're really capable of!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
You asked for it.
Hmph!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT grunts]
[ISSEI thinking]
This fight isn't over.
And I'm not going down without
taking one of his limbs with me.
To do less would be
insulting this man.
I have to give it my all!
[explosion]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT panting]
[SAIRAORG]
What's wrong, Issei?
Is that the best you've got?
Are you really gonna
let me defeat you?
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
No! I'm just getting started!
[DDRAIG echoing]
Boost!
[energy surging]
‐[SAIRAORG grunts]
‐[explosions]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Damn it! It's not good enough.
Without the demonic
power of a bishop,
my attacks are too weak.
[SAIRAORG]
Don't tell me.
Is that your limit?
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
I chose the power of a rook,
so all I can do
is punch it out.
No way am I ready to give up!
Alright, then.
Don't keep me waiting!
[BOTH yelling]
[ASIA]
Issei!
[boom]
Please! You have to power up!
Remember, you're
always the strongest
when you channel
your inner pervert
and touch a woman's boobs!
[wind whistles]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUt]
Huh?
That's right!
He is the Grabbin' Dragon
after all!
Fulfill your role
as the Switch Princess
and whip out
those milk makers!
[ASIA]
We're counting on you.
If it would help, I would
totally let him touch mine,
but I think yours
have a better effect
since they're much bigger!
‐[SAIRAORG] Hmm?
‐[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT] Uh...
Yeah! Asia's right!
The President's fun bumps
are the secret weapon
that allow Issei
to have unlimited power!
"Fun bumps?"
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT groans]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Don't look at me.
Issei's sexual drive is
what makes him so strong!
[SAIRAORG]
Do you really get stronger
by touching a woman's breasts?
I thought that was
just a weird rumor.
It's true, yo.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT groans]
Sounds like it's all
up to you, Rias.
Oh. How can I say no?
And I do want Issei
to unleash his power.
So go on! Grab away!
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT excitedly]
For real?
[cackles delightedly]
What? With your cousin watching!
Whoa! I didn't know you were
into that sorta freaky thang!
Thank you, President!
[moans]
Issei.
So, is this how his fights
always go?
I must say, Asgard culture
is very different.
[RIAS moaning]
[laughing]
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
What's so funny?
Now, I get it! You draw
your power from Rias' knockers!
I'll remember that.
Let's stop our fight here
for today.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
What? I'm not finished!
[SAIRAORG]
That's what she said.
But seriously though,
I'm not either.
However, if we were to continue,
we'd keep fighting
until one of us fell.
It seems like a waste.
Especially when it feels like
you might be on the verge
of some kind of evolution.
[ISSEI‐JUGGERNAUT]
Huh?
[SAIRAORG]
I'm willing to wait until then.
When we can fight
as our best selves.
On that day,
grant me another bout
with the Red Dragon Emperor.
What do you think, Issei?
Are you okay with putting
this battle on hold
until the next Rating Game?
[energy surges]
[ISSEI]
Sure.
[SAIRAORG] Rias! And all those
a part of Rias' house,
the next time we meet
will be on the stage
that leads us to our dreams!
Come! And know
that I'll take you down
with everything I have.
I look forward to the day.
Well, what did you think?
About fighting Sairaorg?
He's a real badass.
And yet, his punches
felt like mine some how.
Indeed, they were.
Sairaorg has trained fervently
to fill the gaps
where he was lacking.
That is how he became so strong,
thus possessing something
other devils do not have.
[ISSEI thinking]
He pushes himself to the limit.
It almost seems foolish,
but I can say that
because I'm the same way.
Our attack is all we have
when it comes
to facing our opponents.
I have to admit, though.
I was impressed.
[ISSEI gasps]
[SIR ZECHS]
Usually when people battle him,
they give up before the bout
is anywhere close to over.
Their demonic power fails,
and they're overwhelmed
by his sheer strength.
And any demon who believes
demonic power equals status
would quickly lose heart.
Especially anyone who comes
from a high‐ranking family.
You know,
I've never properly won
in a Rating Game before.
But next time,
it'll be different.
‐[RIAS] Mother?
‐[VENERANA] Hmm?
[VENERANA] Oh, are you heading
back already?
Yes, Issei and the
other sophomores
need to prepare
for their class trip.
[VENERANA]
I understand.
But don't worry,
we'll be back to visit soon.
‐[MILLICAS] Hey, Issei?
‐[ISSEI] Hmm?
I was wondering,
are you still gonna call Rias
"President" after she graduates?
[ISSEI]
Uh...
[ISSEI thinking]
I never thought about it,
but I guess
after she graduates,
she technically won't be
our President anymore.
But even without that title,
her name is worthy
of so much admiration.
Rias.
[groaning]
I'm so psyched
for the school trip,
that I can't sleep!
Man, this is total ball sacks.
[RIAS]
Oh?
Is the thought of
getting away from me
really that exciting?
That's not what I meant at all!
I just think the trip's
gonna be a lot of fun!
[RIAS] I know, silly.
I'm only teasing you, Issei.
[ISSEI gasps]
Since this is our last night
together for a few days,
I suppose I could
spoil you a bit.
‐Come here!
‐Yes, Breast‐ident!
‐I mean, President! [chuckles]
‐[RIAS giggling]
[RIAS]
Of course, now I'm a totally
different kind of excited!
[ISSEI laughs]
Oh, gimme, gimme!
[RIAS]
Here's your identification.
‐[KIBA] Ah, the rumored ID.
‐[RIAS] Yes.
Devils are required to have
this "free‐pass" on them
while in Kyoto.
It's also handy
for sight‐seeing.
So as long as we have this ID,
we can see all the temples
like Kiyomizu,
Kinkakuji and Ginkakuji?
Yes, that's right!
Basically, it's a pass that
will allow even a devil
to enter the temples in Kyoto.
Go on now
have a good time.
Asia, before I forget,
this is for you.
[ISSEI gasps]
Have fun, and enjoy
one of my favorite cities!
[GROUP]
We will!
See you when we get back.
Take care, Rias.
[IRINA/XENOVIA]
See you later!
[RIAS]
Have a good trip.
We'll bring you a souvenir.
[RIAS]
That's very kind of you.
I should get going too.
[ISSEI grunts]
President?
Oh, Issei, as it turns out,
I'm no better than Akeno.
The truth is I'm going
to miss you terribly.
I've tried to hide it,
but I adore your stupid face.
I find myself missing it
when you're gone
for long periods of time,
and I know that's
totally pathetic.
It's only for a few days.
Besides, you'll have Koneko
and Gasper to keep you company.
Yes, that's true.
Still though, I‐‐
[ISSEI gasps]
Uh, Rias?
I wanted to send
you off with a kiss.
[chuckles] There you again
with that stupid face.
A kiss from me
shouldn't be a surprise.
And yet shockingly,
the kiss somehow managed
to take me by total surprise.
With that,
I'll be able to stand being
apart from you for a few days.
Hurry back, 'kay? Go!
Right! See you later!
[wind whistles]
[ISSEI thinking]
That kiss was amazeballs!
I've got a good feeling
about this school trip.
[chuckles]
[theme song playing]
[ISSEI]
School trip! An abrupt attack!