[AZAZEL]
Issei, using your Sacred Gear,
you can access the emotions
of the previous
Red Dragon Emperors.
Their negative feelings
are so strong,
you could almost
consider them a curse.
If you can find a way
to purge that negativity,
then I believe you'll be able
to trigger a power that's
ultimately stronger, but much
safer than the Juggernaut Drive.
In order to achieve that,
you're going to have
to insert your consciousness
directly into the Sacred Gear.
♪
[ISSEI]
Yo, what's up?
Uh, anyone home?
Guess that's a no.
Okay. How the hell am I supposed
to get through to them?
[train humming]
‐I'm practically naked.
‐[gasps]
[chuckles]
[theme music playing]
Jeez, I get needing
to report in,
but the whole whispering in
the ear thing was just creepy.
I wanted to make sure you
heard me under all that weird,
self‐absorbed mirror‐thinking
you were doing.
I get it. That "naked" thing
was your way of saying
you're unarmed since you had
to hand Durandal over
to the alchemists of the church.
I didn't have much of a choice,
since I'm unable
to control my own aura.
Okay. For right now,
I can lend you Ascalon.
That'd be fantastic,
thank you.
[girls gasp]
Hey there.
Can I sit with you, Issei?
Um, sure.
In case something comes up,
I think it'd be good idea
to compare our plans for Kyoto.
Yeah, we're starting
at Kiyomizu Temple.
Here's our itinerary
or whatever.
Thanks. I think on the third day
we're gonna be in Tenryuji,
so we should find a place
to check in with each other.
Come to think of it,
before your fight with Sairaorg,
I heard something
about how you had to deal
with the Four Great Satans,
is that true?
Ugh! Oh, dude,
you don't even know.
That stuff was super intense.
It completely changed
my view of the underworld.
Of course, it's kind of hard
to take them all seriously
when they're doling out trials
dressed up as Satan Rangers.
And I passed 'em all, but
something kinda weird happened.
‐[gasps]
‐[humming]
[AJUKA]
This is an opportunity.
Currently, there are
many doors available to you,
and you are holding
a very important key.
[gasps]
Now that I think about it,
Lord Beelzebub
also gave me some advice.
‐Is that so?
‐Uh‐huh.
He said in order
to maximize the power
of the Red Dragon Emperor,
I have to work on mastering
the power
of a knight and a rook.
Otherwise, I am screwed,
and I can't beat Sairaorg.
Yes, I completely agree.
I think we could all stand
to get stronger.
True. I'm definitely
gonna need to keep training.
[sighs]
I'd expect nothing less.
Oh, and make sure to give me
a call when you decide
to go buy your souvenirs.
That way we don't get
the same thing.
[chuckles]
Yeah, that'd be a real tragedy.
Since there's
still some time left.
♪
What's up?
Did you miss me? Uh.
Crickets as usual.
Weird, this guy looks
pretty young.
[DDRAIG] Among all the Red
Dragon Emperors, he was born
with the greatest amount
of innate talent.
He even awakened his Juggernaut
Drive at an early age,
but he eventually drowned
in his own power.
That may be the case,
but he still had
something important to him.
I, who shall awaken.
I am the Heavenly Dragon
who stole the principle
of domination for God.
[DDRAIG]
Careful.
It's all good,
not gonna finish it,
not when I barely know
anything about the spell.
Like "mock the infinite"? C'mon.
And what dream
am I supposed to fret over?
[ELSHA] Orphis is that
who is truly infinite.
And Great Red is both
the illusion and the dream.
You laugh at Orphis,
and yet you feel sadness
about your fellow red dragon,
Great Red.
[DDRAIG]
Elsha.
Ddraig, hello there.
‐[DDRAIG] Issei, this is Elsha.
‐[chuckling]
Among all
the previous possessors,
she was the strongest woman.
What was that?
[whispers] Boobies.
[ELSHA]
Why do you look so surprised?
There were two
exceptional possessors,
and I am one of them.
But, we've never met
because I have a nasty habit
of hiding myself away
from the world.
[DDRAIG] Strange, I assumed
you'd be more like Belzard
and never show your face again.
Oh, stop, or you'll hurt
my precious feelings.
So, uh, who the hell's Belzard?
[DDRAIG] He was
the strongest Red Dragon Emperor
among the male possessors.
In fact, he defeated
the White Dragon Emperor twice.
[gasps]
Two times! Are you kidding me?
[laughs]
I'm actually here
to deliver this to you
on behalf of Belzard.
Didn't Beelzebub give you a key
the last time you two spoke?
‐[humming]
‐[gasps]
The Key!
This box contains the potential
of a Red Dragon Emperor.
Man, must be a powerful box.
Indeed, it's also something
that's capable
of destroying who you are.
And for that reason,
it's not a box I suggest
opening without caution.
"The Grabbin' Dragon."
What an interesting song.
Belzard and I watched
that together.
It was the first time I've had
a laugh in quite some time.
[laughs]
Seriously, I don't understand
why Ddraig is
so depressed about it.
I've never seen such an
interesting Red Dragon Emperor!
The Juggernaut Drive spell
has always been eerie,
but thanks to the playful nature
of the Grabbin' Dragon song,
we have finally been able
to push those words
from our hearts.
My and Belzard's last moments
were not what
you would consider pleasant.
That's why we're here.
Our minds are made up.
Open the box. But once you do,
you must shoulder
this burden 'til the bitter end.
It's all or nothing.
No matter what happens,
you must accept it
and always move forward, Issei.
I understand.
[humming]
[grunts]
Huh? Why am I back
on the train now?
Hold up.
Where's the box?
[DDRAIG] No idea, but I do
know you definitely opened it
‐after Elsha gave it to you.
‐No way!
[DDRAIG]
Whatever was inside jumped out.
What the eff did you just say?
Did you see where it went?
Potential?
Here, boy! Come to daddy!
[DDRAIG]
Calm down. It's your potential.
It has no choice but to return.
You are both bound
to each other by destiny.
I can't calm down
when my potential is MIA.
[MATSUDA]
Titties!
[yelps] Matsuda! Get your
filthy hands off of my moobies!
Hey, bro, you do know you're
grabbing dude boobs, don't you?
Sorry, dude,
I was straight trippin'!
All of the sudden I was craving
some tig ol' bitties!
Oh no. Do you realize
that Double D Deficiency
Disorder can kill?
But, don't worry,
it can be cured with porno!
Whoa, really?
Luckily, I have
just what the doctor ordered!
Check out my emergency stash.
Schwing!
[BOTH]
Whoa!
Let's watch them
for Matsuda's sake!
[BOYS]
Yeah! Ye‐Yeah!
God, I hope
they whack it to death.
Yeah, same here.
[BOYS] Porno party! Porno party!
Porno party! Porno party!
FEMALE ANNOUNCER:
You have arrived in Kyoto.
‐[GIRLS gasp]
‐[ISSEI chuckles]
[KIRYUU] All right, you guys.
Pick up those jaws
and let's get moving.
Everyone else has
already left for the hotel.
‐[WOMAN screams]
‐[GROUP gasps]
Stop it! Please!
Sweater stretchers.
I must fondle
her sweater stretchers!
‐What's wrong with you?
‐Cut it out!
Bazongas!
[ISSEI ]Man, Kyoto really brings
out the perv deluxe in people.
[MATSUDA]
Damn, that tower is huge!
Must be a shower not a grower!
[KIRYUU] You tried way too hard
for that joke. Let's go.
[MATSUDA]
Seriously?
I feel like such a baller
right now, yo!
It's so fancy.
Yeah, just move it along
before you block traffic.
Okay. Listen up, everyone.
Miss Rossweisse
has an announcement.
[ROSSWEISSE chuckles]
Thanks, Azazel.
The hundred yen shop is located
underneath Kyoto station!
Go forth and save yourself
some money! [continues speaking]
[AZAZEL] Also, stay out
of trouble and all that jazz.
She's just gonna keep going,
so you can head
to your rooms now.
A high‐class hotel owned
by the Gremorys?
This room's gonna be bangin'!
[bag thuds]
♪
What the hell?
This room sucks total ass!
[BOTH laugh]
Damn sucka, you got
the lamest digs in the hotel!
Huh? Are you saying
your rooms are better?
♪
Well, I guess this is
how the school managed
to pull off the lodging budget.
I really hate you guys.
Hello, Issei, are you in here?
Oh, Miss Rossweisse!
[whispers]
This is super unfair.
Well, this is the room that
Rias had prepared for us.
She wanted to make sure
we have a place to meet
if there's an emergency.
Makes sense. Wait, so why
am I the one getting screwed?
We greatly appreciate
your sacrifice, Issei.
By the way, you boys have
free time this afternoon,
so feel free
to go explore a bit,
but stay out of trouble, okay?
‐[MATSUDA] Yes, ma'am!
‐[MOTOHAMA] Yes, ma'am!
So what you guys wanna do?
I've got it!
Let's go strut our stuff
around Kyoto
with the class hotties.
‐Aw yeah!
‐Sounds good!
♪
[ASIA gasps]
Aw, check out
the little stone foxies!
I wish I had brought
more money with me.
[IRINA]
They're super presh!
[GIRLS giggle]
‐Be right back!
‐Okay!
Xenovia!
Look at this, isn't it cute?
‐Yeah, it's adorable.
‐[camera clicking]
Is it a Japanese monster?
[KIRYUU] Hey, aren't you gonna
take any pictures of me?
If I did that, you'd probably
crack the lens or something.
I'll have you know
the camera loves me.
I am a natural model.
Snap a pic and you'll see.
Behold! I'm a tiger,
fierce and gorgeous!
My eyes are gonna melt outta
my face, stop, I beg of you!
♪
This statue keeps demons at bay.
Normally, we wouldn't
be able to get close
because of the power
it projects.
But thanks to this special pass,
I guess it won't be a problem!
Huh?
Issei, you're holding us up!
Move it or lose it, bro!
[MOTOHAMA]
Come on! But stay outta my pics,
'cause this film
is reserved for babes!
[ISSEI]
Whatever, man!
[ALL chattering]
[ISSEI] Jeez, now I get why it's
called "The Thousand Gates,"
it feels like
it goes on for miles.
[KIRYUU]
This is only the entrance.
We have to pass through
all these gates
and climb the mountain
to reach the top.
[MOTOHAMA groans]
Please kill me.
‐[leaves rustle]
‐[gasps]
Sorry, but I need
to go look at something!
[GIRLS gasp]
[panting]
Phew!
Finally made it to the end!
Dear whoever,
please make me the harem king!
‐[KUNOU] You are not from Kyoto.
‐[gasps]
Uh, hey guys,
what's with the masks?
[gasps]
♪
Those ears. Is she a fox?
Stupid outsider! How dare you!
You'd better return mother
to me right now!
Huh?
♪
[ISSEI] What are you talking
about? I don't know your mom,
and I definitely
don't know where she is.
Filthy liar!
I'll teach you to try
and deceive me!
[yelps, grunts]
[panting]
Xenovia. Irina!
Are you okay, Issei?
These people
must be youkai, right?
Please, be careful.
Impure beings of evil!
I will never forgive you
for what you've done!
Asia! The Substitute
acknowledgment card!
Okay!
Here we go!
Promotion, pawn to knight!
Take them down!
We're guests in Kyoto!
Try not to harm our opponents
or the surrounding area!
[GIRLS]
You got it!
[DDRAIG]
Boost! Boost!
Boost! Explosion!
Listen to me, vile outsiders,
we will retreat for now,
but this is far from over!
You will return my mother!
[ISSEI]
What was that about?
[AZAZEL] I wonder why they chose
to attack you at the shrine.
[ISSEI] No idea,
but I wish I knew the answer.
Do you think we should report
all this to the President?
It's hard to say since we still
don't know the whole situation,
but I'll be sure
to report it properly.
Cool, sounds like a plan.
[indistinct chattering]
[chuckles]
As a school teacher
and as a woman,
I cannot allow you
to go any further, Issei!
Look, I know we're normally
on the same team,
but I'm not
backing down on this.
I'm gonna sneak a peek
at that hooter haven!
I guess that means
we're enemies, then!
No way, are your attacks
actually stronger than usual?
You don't get it.
If I could just see
my female classmates'
super droopers,
only then will I have fulfilled
my true destiny as a man!
Come on! You see and touch
Rias and Akeno's
naked bodies every single day.
Isn't that enough for you?
Sorry, but no.
I'm a cleavage connoisseur!
[sighs] You've left me
with no choice, Issei.
Remember, I can always
ask Saji to change
into his Dragon King form.
That would put a stop
to this madness.
Whoa, seriously?
Like you'd go that far?
Gah, why ya gotta be
such a control freak!
You know, I hate to bring
this up. That's probably why
you can't land yourself
a boyfriend. Too damn strict!
[gasps]
W‐W‐W‐W‐‐ What did you say?
[crying] Wow,
that's a low blow even for you!
It's not like I want to die as
a lonely, decrepit old virgin!
I'd love to have
a super‐hot boyfriend to sex up
whenever the mood
strikes me, but no!
Not good, I totally
just triggered this broad.
You are past
the point of forgiveness.
Yup, I'm totally screwed.
‐[shouts]
‐[DDRAIG] Boost! Boost!
Boost! Explosion!
‐[explosion]
‐Huh?
Game over! Dress Break!
[screaming]
Aw, yeah. Jiggly jackpot!
‐[gasps]
‐Oops, sorry!
I guess I took things
a little too far, didn't I?
[ROSSWEISSE] I can't believe
you! This shirt was a steal
at 50% off, you jerk!
Uh, say what now?
Sure, it was cheap, but it was
also like, really cute!
Oh no!
Now I'll never land a man.
Yeah, sure, blame me.
Shut your face, Issei!
Tearing up a girl's clothes
is just plain awful,
and fiscally irresponsible!
Not to mention totally wasteful!
As your teacher,
there's no way I'm going
‐to let this atrocity slide!
‐[ISSEI] Well, at least I got
to see someone's
fun bags tonight.
They're not bad, almost as nice
as the president's!
[sighs]
‐What is it Akeno?
‐Oh, I was just wondering
why Issei only gets stronger
when he touches your breasts.
‐What?
‐[AKENO] Is it the size, maybe?
No way, besides yours are
much larger. Right, Koneko?
I rarely stare at your tee‐tas,
but if it's really
that important to you,
then sure, Akeno's are bigger.
[AKENO]
You really think so?
Perhaps it all comes down
‐to the shape, then.
‐Hey, don't.
Quit it! I'm serious!
[AKENO]
Or could it be the softness?
[gasps] Stop!
I said that's enough!
‐Knock it off!
‐[AKENO laughs]
‐Let me feel the left one.
‐[RIAS] It feels the same!
Quit being so stubborn,
I'm just curious!
All I want to know is why
Issei prefers yours over mine!
Well, it's because
he has good taste, obviously!
[AKENO] Is that what
you call it? I disagree!
[RIAS] Not that I can say
the same for you.
‐[water splashes]
‐[RIAS yelps]
♪
What has gotten into you?
[giggles] Nothing.
You're the one
getting all riled up, Rias.
[RIAS] She keeps this up, she'll
be dead before Issei gets home.
Doesn't your sex drive
have any kind of "off" button?
Bueller? Hello, McFly?
‐Yeah. Very nice.
‐[AZAZEL] Anyone here?
[both gasp]
[ISSEI]
Azazel!
Sorry, I didn't mean
to interrupt your fun.
[gasps]
Uh, nothing's happening!
Is there something
we can do for you?
I'm supposed
to bring you to a meeting,
as requested
by the Devil Queen.
‐Oh hey, what's up, Issei?
‐Yo, Saji, how's Kyoto so far?
Ugh, it's kinda super lame.
Being on student council means
spending my time
helping teachers.
Yeah, that totally sounds
like a giant bag of dildos.
Here! Oh my gosh, the chicken
is, like, way delicious!
Everyone, dig in
and help yourselves!
Lady Leviathan? Wait,
what brings you out to Kyoto?
Oh, work stuff. I'm here
because I'm forging an alliance
with the youkai,
so it's strictly business.
Unfortunately, I'm afraid
something rather terrible
‐has happened, so...
‐Like what exactly?
Well, the leader of the Kyoto
youkai has disappeared.
More specifically, she's a
nine‐tailed fox who's missing.
No way.
‐Then the attack...
‐At the Fushimi Shrine...
It must have been about that.
[SAJI] Sounds like I missed out
on a good time today.
Azazel filled me in earlier,
and I believe
that's what's happened.
This news
doesn't bode well for us.
More than likely,
the people behind all this...
Are probably the Chaos Brigade.
[ISSEI]
Not those douchers.
Damn it.
It'll be tough to do anything
with the students here.
They've really got us this time.
[LEVIATHAN]
There are other youkai
here in Kyoto
that are willing to help us.
If we utilize those contacts,
then we may be able
to do something.
That sounds like a start.
[ISSEI]
Okay, so, what should we do?
For right now,
try to enjoy your school trip.
[ISSEI]
Huh? Seriously?
I'll let you know
if I need you.
Aren't you kids supposed
to be out making memories,
or something stupid like that?
Just let the adults handle this
business for the time being.
You brats try
and have fun in Kyoto.
‐Wow, thanks a lot, Azazel.
‐For sure!
It's a once‐in‐a‐lifetime trip,
after all!
We should all have a little fun!
That's enough chit‐chat for now.
It's time
for some delicious food!
[ISSEI] I'm down for that!
Let's stuff our faces! Dig in.
[ALL]
Thanks for the food!
♪
[ISSEI] The Chaos Brigade wants
to destroy our current system.
What a bunch of ass hats.
You know they aren't
just made up
of the Old Satan faction either.
There's probably others.
Looks like there's never a dull
moment, even on a school trip.
That's true.
What we should do is try
and prepare ourselves
for the worst‐case scenario.
Yes. I kind of wish Rias
could be here, though.
[ISSEI]
I want to protect the Kyoto
that the President
loves so much.
[theme music playing]
[ISSEI]
"The Party of Heroes"!