[bullet ricochets]
[gasping]
Marlya. Hang on.
Explain yourself.
What the hell did you do?
♪
[roaring]
[grunts, sighs]
[snarls]
[sighs]
[FREE]
Now I get it.
Whatever damage we do,
is inflicted back on us.
-[growling]
-[SWEETIE chuckles]
[SWEETIE] Well done, Skriker.
Good fairy.
[FREE] She was trouble
enough by herself,
but now I’ve also got to contend
with that bizarre fairy.
-[BOTH grunting]
-[metal scraping]
[snarling]
-[grunting]
-[FREE gasps]
[gunfire]
Oh wow.
Is that some new popular dance?
-I hate you.
-[SWEETIE] Why’d you stop?
Please, continue.
Only if you’d care to join,
Sweetie.
[SWEETIE chuckles]
[MARLYA]
Ow.
The dust must cause the damage.
It’s everywhere.
[FAIRIES growling]
Are you sure
you still want to play?
If you’re not in the mood,
I can take this off your hands.
[MARLYA] I won’t let you steal
the Black Fairy Tome!
[gasps]
You fool!
I was going to spare you!
[SKRIKER snarls]
Fall back, Marlya!
-[SWEETIE groaning]
-[SKRIKER growling]
You will not outlast me!
I must say,
that look suits you.
Being protected by a girl.
Oh, shut up!
You’ll regret this, I swear!
We showed her, didn’t we, Free?
The Black Fairy Tome’s ours.
Yeah, thanks to you.
[MARLYA winces]
Easy there.
You’re hurt.
Not bad, huh, Partner?
You did good, kid.
[MARLYA chuckles]
[sighs]
[RAY]
Burn it all!
[MAN] Why? Ray Dawn?
Why’re you doing this?
[BOTH panting]
[SOLDIER A]
They must’ve gone this way!
[SOLDIER B]
Don’t let them escape!
[SOLDIER C]
Burn the entire forest!
[YOUNG MARLYA crying]
I’ll draw the soldiers
in the other direction.
Use that time to escape.
[YOUNG MARLYA]
But if you do that, you’ll be...
Don’t worry.
You know how fast I am.
They’ll never be
able to catch up.
I’ll be alright.
Stay here.
Don’t go, Ver.
Ver!
[YOUNG VERONICA]
It’s okay. Trust me.
I won’t let
anything bad happen.
[birds chirping]
♪
[gasps softly]
[ethereal whispering]
So many fairies.
[inhales sharply]
Shh.
[YOUNG VERONICA]
Your name’s Marlya, isn’t it?
[YOUNG MARLYA]
If you knew that, then why...
[YOUNG VERONICA]
Why what?
[YOUNG MARLYA]
I mean. I’m just...
♪
[YOUNG VERONICA]
It’s okay. You can trust me.
I won’t let anything bad happen.
♪
Don’t go.
This isn’t Sweetie’s blood.
Axel’s then?
Did someone carry him
out of here?
[birds shrieking]
[knock on door]
Did you have any luck
with the investigation?
I managed to uncover
a few clues.
The party responsible
might’ve escaped,
but at least we were able
to recover the Black Fairy Tome.
Speaking of which,
your colleague is still asleep.
[FREE]
I expected as much.
Thank you for
letting her rest here.
Think nothing of it.
Having Dorothea in my debt
could prove
extremely useful later on.
[laughs softly]
Would it be okay
if we remained your guests
until she wakes up?
Certainly.
Stay as long as you need.
♪
[DIESE]
Does that bring this inspection
to a close, Nein Auler?
[NEIN]
Yes. Thank you, Duke Hybranz.
Why so formal?
You and I go way back.
It’s Schwarz Diese, please.
[NEIN]
The war is over,
and while I may not be
your subordinate any longer,
I’m afraid I’m in no position
to be informal.
[DIESE]
Hmm.
I assure you,
there’s nothing here
I wouldn’t want
your people to see.
I hope I’ve made
that crystal clear.
The government will receive
my full report.
[DIESE]
Hmm.
If I break the law,
I don’t leave evidence.
The same is true
if I choose to obey it.
You’re aware
how pointless this is.
Regardless, sir,
we simply carry out our duty.
[DIESE exhales sharply]
You weren’t kidding.
You haven’t changed.
[NEIN]
Thank you for your cooperation.
We’ll be taking our leave.
[DIESE]
Of course.
I hope I was
able to be of service.
-[grunting]
-[heavy wheels moving]
[PATTY sighs]
Made it! How are ya?
[WAITER]
Can I take your order?
Sure. One fresh water.
You only want water, miss?
Fresh water, you stooge.
[WAITER]
Coming right up.
If he brings me a glass
and it’s stale,
-he’s a dead man.
-[SWEETIE] I’m glad to see
you haven’t changed
one bit, Patricia.
[SWEETIE laughs softly]
It’s Patty.
Sweets.
What incredible luck
you were in Isharat already.
And here I was thinking
I would have to send for you.
Jonathan.
Is he in the city too?
He’s around.
So what did you have in mind?
Your specialty.
Tying up loose ends.
[moaning]
[gasps sharply]
Why do I feel so drained?
You’re here.
[groans]
Finally woke up.
Guess so,
but how long
was I out for?
[FREE]
A while.
-Almost an entire day.
-That long, huh?
Things could have been a lot
worse than how they turned out.
Don’t push yourself too hard.
I’ll try not to, doctor.
You can sit up?
Yes. It’s just.
Where’s the Black Fairy Tome?
[chuckles] You mean this?
[MARLYA gasps softly]
[FREE]
You’ll receive the credit.
But it’s all for nothing
if the Tome proves
to be a counterfeit.
You mean it isn’t
the real thing?
I’ll have to deliver it
to the Ministry of Fairies
for appraisal first.
We’ll know after that.
Out of all the texts,
the Black Tome
is by far the most valuable.
It’s not uncommon for forgeries
to be bought and sold.
[MARLYA groans]
-Like at mafia auctions.
-[FREE] Yeah.
They become the showpiece
whenever they’re featured.
Like the one we were guarding.
Seems it’s necessary.
There’s been trouble
at a number of auctions
these last few years.
[MARLYA]
Yeah, I heard something similar.
I didn’t hear of any robberies
at Gui Carlin
gatherings up to that point.
We didn’t have any detailed
information either.
Your friend.
You thought she was the one
hitting the auctions.
[MARLYA]
I didn’t have any proof,
but that’s what I figured.
There were some connections.
[FREE]
To the mafia, you mean?
[MARLYA]
Then she showed up,
and came for the
Black Fairy Tome.
Then took off with it.
[FREE sighs]
[FREE]
Who knows.
Maybe that’s
how this made it
all the way to Isharat.
And if that’s true,
then Cain and Damien
might know about her.
You want to know
how we got our hands
on the Black Fairy Tome.
No surprise, but...
[DAMIEN]
My apologies.
That’s something
we cannot reveal.
You can’t or you won’t?
[CAIN sighs]
Is this an official inquiry
from Dorothea?
[chuckling]
Not at all.
Our business is concluded.
You reported to the Ministry
that you had
the Black Fairy Tome
in your possession
and so they sent us.
Our only interest was
retrieving the text from you.
Then this
is a simple chat.
Since it isn’t government
business, I’ll say this.
There are things
we can reveal to you
and things we cannot.
Look at it this way.
We have to protect our sources.
Private Fairy scholars like us
are barely allowed to exist
since we share the results
of our research
with Unified Zesskia.
But after the war,
I seem to recall
the Ministry
offering jobs
to people in your field.
I was too low on the ladder
for them to even notice me.
Cain on the other hand received
multiple invitations to join.
By the time the war ended,
I was already an old man.
I wanted to spend my remaining
years free of bureaucracy.
Well, In that case,
could you
tell me just one thing?
Veronica Thorn.
Have you heard that name before?
Regrettably,
it’s not ringing a bell.
-Damien. You?
-No.
I’ve not. Sorry.
[MARLYA]
I see.
If you’ll excuse me.
♪
[birds squawking]
-[bell ringing]
-[indistinct chatter]
[voracious chewing]
[FREE]
You don’t need to wolf it down.
We have plenty of time.
Our train isn’t leaving
for a while.
How am I supposed to get better
if I don’t eat?
Also, I wasn’t wolfing.
[FREE sighs]
Hey, not half bad.
-[MARLYA] Those people.
-Huh?
I’m going to assume you’re
referring to Cain and Damien.
-Yeah.
-Ah.
I know I should be grateful
they let me stay there,
but they’re liars.
That’s quite the accusation.
-You got any proof?
-No, but you!
[FREE] Can’t blame them
for concealing their sources.
[MARLYA groans]
How else can they survive?
Like they said,
being a private
fairy scholar is tough, so...
[MARLYA]
Then maybe they should join
the Ministry of Fairies
or whatever.
And stop complaining.
They don’t want to.
Once the chain’s
around their neck,
there are things
they can’t do.
[PATTY]
Am I glad to put this down!
[BOTH] Huh?
Please, don’t pay me any mind.
[WAITER]
What’ll it be?
[PATTY] I’ll have a glass
of fresh water.
Water. That’s it?
[PATTY]
And make sure it’s fresh.
-Of course, madame.
-As for me,
I’ll have love and despair,
back and forth.
-Served at their most extreme.
-[WAITER] Sir?
[PATTY] Just bring him
something off the menu
that doesn’t take
long to prepare.
[WAITER]
Right away.
Hi.
[FREE]
Uh...
[FREE chuckles]
[MARLYA groans]
[MARLYA]
Where did...?
-[PATTY chuckles]
-[FREE] Huh?
[PATTY groans, chuckles]
I’ll be seeing you around.
She left? What about her water?
-[FREE grunts]
-[MARLYA gasps]
[MARLYA]
What is it?
-Ta-ta.
-Hey, stop!
Wait, where are you going?
-[FREE] She stole it!
-[gasps]
[MARLYA panting]
Think you’ll be able
to keep up?
-Yes, sir.
-Stay close.
♪
This church hasn’t been
in use for years.
What’s down there?
A network of endless tunnels.
There’s a maze of old water
and sewer passageways
beneath Isharat.
Crypts as well,
if I remember right.
Oh, great.
I think someone’s living here.
[FREE]
Looks like it.
[MARLYA]
A person!
Formerly.
[MARLYA whimpers]
-[gun clicks]
-[FREE inhales sharply]
-[MARLYA gasps]
-[gunfire]
Get inside of there!
[MARLYA]
With him?
Do it, or you’ll both be dead!
Howl, Red Hood!
[roaring]
[explosion]
[MARLYA]
I can’t see anything!
Yeah, and neither can they.
Just stay put.
[RED HOWL snarls]
[FREE]
You want me to follow you.
What for?
What’re they after?
Doesn’t matter if they’re
with Arcame or Gui Carlin.
If they were only after
the Black Fairy Tome,
they could’ve gotten away.
Are they after me?
[FREE]
Get off him!
[PATTY screaming]
[PATTY grunts]
[screams]
Just who is this bitch?
-[objects crashing]
-[PATTY grunting]
[MARLYA]
I’m unlucky.
I’m convinced of it.
-[bones clatter]
-[MARLYA gasps]
Forgive me.
[MARLYA]
I’ve been a little disaster.
Since the day I was born.
[MARLYA gasps]
It was pitch black
only a second ago.
So, who?
-[gunshot]
-[rifle cocks]
[MAN]
Where do you think you’re going?
[gunshot]
[rifle cocks]
[breathing heavily]
[MARLYA]
I used to envy Ver.
She was constantly
surrounded by people.
Always laughing and radiant.
She had friends.
A family that was
actually related to her.
[MAN, echoing]
Patty was clear.
I’m to capture you.
Seems she means
to use you as bait
should Free Underbar
prove too formidable.
You might not be able to tell
upon first meeting her,
but she is quite cautious.
You’re behind me,
aren’t you?
-[MAN grunts]
-[metal scraping]
The more you keep resisting,
the more beautiful
my work will be.
I have a suspicion
you’ll wind up
being one of my
finest masterpieces.
Lady.
[MARLYA]
What the hell’s going on?
[panting]
[eerie chuckling]
The name’s Jonathan,
and I’m a true artist!
-[metal pinging]
-[MARLYA yelps]
Oh, but whatever you do,
don’t refer to me
as “Jon.”
I want you to call me
Jonathan,
or Jona if you prefer.
[grunts]
♪
[MARLYA]
I’m through running!
-[JONATHAN grunts]
-[MARLYA yelps]
[gunshot]
Don’t you realize,
pain is a blessing, lady?
[screams]
I have to hurt you.
The more I do,
the closer it brings me
to the truth!
[MARLYA]
This guy’s insane.
Nothing he’s says
makes any sense.
My fairy.
I still can’t summon it!
Let me clarify
what I mean by “art”.
It’s the act of understanding
another person!
[gun clattering]
[MARLYA groans]
[JONATHAN]
I want to be someone
who understands you
inside and out.
[glass shattering]
-[glass shatters]
-[JONATHAN gasps]
[MARLYA gasps]
Ver!
[YOUNG MARLYA crying]
Everything’s alright.
Don’t cry, Marlya.
[MARLYA gasps]
[metal scrapes]
[YOUNG VERONICA] Trust me.
I won’t let anything bad happen.
[MARLYA] Ver!
Am I a little disaster
like everyone says?
[VERONICA]
Because I’m still empty inside.
It’s your fault, all of it!
Ray Dawn!