[MARLYA]
To make a long story short,
I've grown convinced
that I'm unlucky.
[FREE]
In the end, I suppose I'm lucky.
[RED HOOD growls]
[FAIRY TECHNICIAN]
We'll remove the fairy organ
from Red Hood and surgically
implant it inside you.
[RED HOOD roars]
[FREE gasps]
[FAIRY TECHNICIAN]
You volunteered and were chosen
for the procedure based
on your capacity
to become a Fairy Soldier.
This was your choice.
Glory to our kingdom of Ledrad.
And glory to our leader,
Majesty Olbany.
[FREE grunts]
[MARLYA] The person who
raised me ended up dying.
I had no one.
As for my mother and father,
they both died
the day I was born.
People called me
the "little disaster."
[MARLYA] Anyone who gets close
to me meets a tragic end.
I was born unlucky.
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[RED FAIRY SOLDIER A groans]
[FAIRY SOLDIERS grunting]
Fire!
[RED SOLDIERS gasp, scream]
[roars]
[grunts]
[FREE yelling]
[FREE grunts]
[FREE groans]
[NORKA growls]
[screaming]
For your crimes,
you will bleed.
[WOLF]
No! Run!
[coughs]
[JET panting]
Jet! No!
[FREE]
Don't die.
Wake up!
[FREE]
This isn't real.
Come on, Jet, open your eyes!
You're not dead!
[FREE cries]
[FREE]
No denying it.
I'm lucky all right.
In the worst way possible.
[MARLYA]
Mm...
[CHIMA chirps]
[FREE whistles]
[NEIN] To recap, your
year-long infiltration
into Gui Carlin ended in
failure, due to the appearance
of a fairy-wielding
woman named Veronica.
You then returned
with a young lady
who has ties to the
aforementioned woman.
Is that the gist of it,
Free Underbar?
Did I leave anything
important out?
[FREE] I'd say it's
an accurate summary.
[NEIN]
Marlya Noel.
In your report, you mention
she might be fairy-possessed.
[FREE] Mm... Yes, however
there's no evidence
she underwent a fairy organ
transplant like we did.
[FREE groaning]
A fairy primordial directly
possessing a human host.
[NEIN]
It shouldn't be possible.
[FREE] Yet that seems to
be the only explanation.
Uh!
I'd rather this matter didn't
leave my office, understood?
Your report will need
to be rewritten.
[sighs]
[NEIN] You're not pleased with
your commanding officer's order?
I'll get right on it.
[footsteps]
[door opens, closes]
[NEIN grunts]
[IZEM] That's the limit as far
as this place is concerned.
There aren't many customers
who place orders this large.
Good thing, too.
Or there'd be war again.
I could do without
another war.
Hard enough surviving
the last one.
Though our profits
would skyrocket.
Huh?
See ya at the rendezvous
point then?
[WOLF]
Yeah.
Hey, Free.
Mind if I open the window?
Go ahead.
So you just wanted to
find this Veronica.
That was the only reason
for joining the mafia?
I guess.
Because she's a target
for Dorothea.
You realize that fact,
don't you?
[MARLYA]
Regulation.
But... If you choose to stick
with this line of work,
I'm sure you'll run
into her again.
[MARLYA]
Next time, it'll be as enemies.
Veronica from Suna
is gone forever.
Forget her.
[MARLYA]
I couldn't do that, Ver.
Ever.
[gasps]
How much further?
My poor backside...
Did ya say something?
Nothing at all!
The Arcame mafia
deals extensively
in artificial fairies. They're
even manufacturing them.
So, our mission is to
expose and take down
their illegal operation?
[FREE]
According to our intel,
a large transaction
is occurring nearby.
We want to secure the contraband
and identify the buyer.
Artificial fairies--
they're supposed to fight
in the place of humans?
That's right.
But the War of Unification
ended years ago.
Why would anybody need them now?
Makes you think there's a chance
the war never really ended.
Oh! Welcome to
the observatory, sir.
You too, Marlya.
Any movement so far?
I'm afraid not.
Good to see you,
Mr. Tova. And...
Quiet, please.
You're distracting.
[SERGE] Heh, we should
do what she says.
You don't want to make
Klara angry, trust me.
I'm a bit of an expert when
it comes to making her mad.
Still too loud.
What'd I say?
Soul-shaking. [laughs]
Why're you laughing then?
Oh, and by the way,
you can call me Serge.
And as for her...
Klara will work just fine.
[gasps]
Here they come.
[SERGE grunts]
[creaking]
[KLARA]
One person's getting out.
[FREE]
Can you see the cargo?
[SERGE]
Looks like there's more coming.
[gasps]
[FREE]
Three vehicles?
Given their size, I'd say each
of those transports could hold
ten artificial fairies.
Thirty total.
[KLARA]
In the plaza!
Someone else.
I see red!
They're a Fairy Soldier!
[FREE]
What?
I can't make out their
face from this distance.
[KLARA gasps]
Is everything all right?
[KLARA]
Yes.
Whoever that person is, they
were looking in this direction.
Or rather, my fairy's...
We may've been spotted.
What do you say we
rush the caravan,
seize the merchandise,
and call it a night?
We will only as a last resort.
Hold.
Somethin' wrong?
[WOLF]
No.
Wait. One of them is moving.
It's the Fairy Soldier.
[FREE]
On it.
Hey. We're going to ground
level to track them.
[MARLYA] I'm... sorry.
Were you talking to me?
[SERGE] We might be playing
right into their hands.
Serge and Klara, stay here and
continue surveilling the plaza.
Are you comin' or what?
Huh. Years have passed,
and it's still the same.
It looks like the ruins of
some destroyed large city.
I take it you've been
to this place before?
When it was a war zone.
A long time ago.
[FREE]
Where the hell did they go?
Uh.
[MARLYA]
These tracks are still fresh.
They're nearby.
Wait up.
Then they come to a
sudden stop right here.
How?
Someone just passed by.
They might be backtracking.
What does that mean?
You see bears do it often.
And other smart animals.
They walk back over
their own prints.
I get it.
While we run in circles,
they make their escape.
[FREE, MARLYA panting]
[FREE]
Move, Serge!
[KLARA]
Get down!
[FREE grunts]
[gasps] It can't be!
[FREE]
Wolfran!
No. I should stay outta this.
You're an errand boy
for the mafia?
How pathetic.
What happened to you?
Answer me!
What does your family
think of you now?
Your wife and your daughter?
[WOLF] I see you still don't
know when to stop yapping.
[FREE gasps]
[gasps] Not good!
[FREE]
Marlya!
[MARLYA grunts]
[FITCHER grunts]
[MARLYA yelps]
This fairy is...
[groans]
Fall back, now!
Hope you didn't forget
about me, sir!
[WOLF gasps]
Weaklings like to swarm.
[FREE]
Damn it!
Uh.
Is it trying to protect her?
It's all right. He isn't
going to hurt me.
[panting] What is this feeling?
[FREE]
Can you stand?
I think. [panting]
Who is he?
We were comrades
during the great war.
As long as I've known him,
he's been ruthless and cunning.
Still, it isn't like him
to run from a fight.
[SERGE]
Sir!
Pursue the target!
I'll cover you with sniper fire
while Klara spots for me!
Then we're going to need
to relocate quickly!
Lead the way.
You good to go?
It's for the job,
right? I'm ready.
Yes, ma'am.
[BOTH gasp]
Looks like our
operation is blown.
Dorothea already knew
about the meeting place.
So what're we
supposed to do now?
Call it off?
We fight back.
There's a sniper. Be careful.
[IZEM]
They were meant to be sold,
so only three are tuned up.
[WOLF]
It'll be enough.
[whistle blows]
[FREE gasps]
You okay?
Just fine.
Good.
There's three of them.
Why isn't it...?
Your fairy took a lot
of damage back there.
It needs to rest.
What should I do then?
You provide covering fire.
They're not people.
Shoot to kill!
[FREE grunting]
[gasps]
Hitting it's no problem,
but where do I hit it?
Well, Wolfran?! Show yourself!
Your range is 620.
[SERGE]
Got it.
[FREE grunts]
Fire!
[MARLYA]
Huh? He kids around,
but Serge is an incredible shot.
[FREE grunts]
Get moving!
[MARLYA]
Yeah. That's a good idea!
Lose your nerve?
Try me, creep.
Ironic, isn't it?
Facing each other
here of all places.
You don't actually think
you can keep up with me.
[FREE grunts]
[RED HOOD howls]
[IZEM grunting]
[WOLF]
So, you're not dead... Yet.
[IZEM]
Huh?!
Why're you doin' this?
I used to be a
soldier too, y'know.
If I was caught,
I wouldn't have talked.
You have to believe me.
They all say the same thing.
--[IZEM gasps]
--Sorry.
[gunshot]
[creaking]
You're not getting away from me!
Marlya!
Meet up with Klara and Serge!
But!
Think you can outrun
me with a transport?
Wolfran!
Here goes nothing...
Start talkin', pal!
Tell me who did this to you?
Don't be stupid.
Never should've trusted him.
Damn...
[FREE grunts, laughs]
I don't know why I'm surprised.
Leave no trace behind, huh?
Still thorough as ever, I see.
All this time and he
hasn't changed one bit.
So that's how you
want to play it?
[exhales]
[FREE]
Plenty of room.
Enough to manufacture
artificial fairies.
[MARCO]
Securing the Black Fairy Tome
is a matter of grave
concern for us.
[MARLYA]
Don't move!
[SWEETIE] Young lady,
you may call me Bitter.