[GILBERT]
Hmm?
They're standing right here.
This is my present.
These are two agents
from Dorothea.
-[GILBERT grunts]
-[pistols cocking]
♪
How generous, but what exactly
am I supposed to do with them?
Whatever you'd like,
it doesn't matter to me.
I'm sure you'll be able
to think of something.
[bellowing]
The signal!
Let's move!
[whooshing]
[roaring]
-Traitor!
-[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[whooshing]
Ugh!
[GILBERT groaning]
I'd think twice
before pulling the trigger.
Unless of course you don't care
what happens to Gilbert.
Drop your weapons, now!
[SWEETIE] See what happens
when I don't get my way?
You're the last one I expected
to ally with Dorothea.
Have you no shame?
[chuckles]
Well Hanns, until we meet
again tomorrow.
Yep.
[HANNS]
Hmm?
Can we help you?
You're Hanns Efmed?
I don't believe
we've been introduced.
I'm Daniel Keys
with the Security Bureau.
We'd like to have a word
regarding the malfunctions
with the Zern Ones.
Please come with us.
Chief, no.
Gilbert loves his corridors.
Serge and I will go this way.
You take that hall, Ozz.
Got it.
[GILBERT]
There's no one else alive
who'd attempt something
so brazen.
Please, go on.
Sounds like the unit's
already stormed the mansion.
Let's wait for them
to catch up to us.
Fat chance.
Gilbert here is a clever man.
He probably has something
hidden up his sleeve.
I can attest with certainty,
I'll never be as cunning
as you, Sweetie.
You girls should watch out.
[GILBERT] You're working
alongside a born swindler.
It looks like there's no
other way out of this room.
But where is it?
I don't see the Black Four.
You're right. There's nothing
in here that even resembles it.
[SWEETIE]
Well, Gilbert?
Continue the tour.
-[GILBERT] What are you...?
-I'm doing you a favor.
Wouldn't you rather have them
babysitting you?
[KLARA]
Stop!
-You're kidding!
-I swear, you'll pay for this!
I should've known.
[MARLYA]
It's no use.
It won't open!
Where'd Sweetie run to?
She took a secret passage
through here!
Surely there's more than one.
[TED]
Wait, where are you going?
[CHASE]
What happened?
Tell me why they're taking
him away!
[CHASE] Calm down.
Where's Hanns?
The Security Bureau took him!
[CHASE]
Daniel already made his move?
Didn't waste any time.
Doesn't seem to be working.
[SERGE]
Must be set up so it won't open
if you shut it
from the other side.
I'm glad you're safe.
-Don't tease me.
-I wasn't.
I meant it.
[FREE]
This way.
Here's what we're looking for.
-[explosion]
-[roaring]
Just how many tunnels
does this place have?
Let's go.
Right!
It's still here?
The Black Four.
She must've left it behind.
Looks like it.
But where is Sweetie?
She has to be close.
He still hasn't confessed yet.
Try to keep it short.
[CHASE]
Sure.
Thanks.
[door opens]
All right, Hanns.
You need to tell me the truth.
They're saying I'm the one
who sabotaged the new models.
[HANNS scoffs]
-Comedians, all of 'em.
-Think so?
The Zern Ones were supposed
to be a symbol of unification
after the war ended.
Their image is tarnished.
This is serious.
[HANNS sighs]
Yeah.
Guess so.
Listen.
I need you tell me
what you know.
[LEFT TECHNICIAN gasps]
[RIGHT TECHNICIAN]
What is it?
[LEFT TECHNICIAN]
Assistant Vice-Minister.
Take a look.
[GRIFF]
Hmm.
It appears as though
some kind of device
was installed
then later removed.
Seems like the only explanation.
How odd.
So Bitter Sweet
managed to escape.
We were going to place her
under arrest,
after we used her
to retrieve the Black Four.
But...
She left it behind instead.
Looks like both sides
managed to achieve
what
they wanted out of the deal.
That makes it a draw.
Director Nein!
We're in the middle
of a briefing!
I'm sorry,
but word from East End:
they uncovered evidence
someone's definitely tampered
with the new models.
[SETT]
Truly, regrettable news.
We must realize, even though
the culprit was on the inside,
the new model still has a frame
that can be made to malfunction,
meaning...
There's only one question
I need answered.
Can we say with
absolute certainty the Zern Ones
will be able to protect
his Imperial Majesty?
Based on all the information
we have available.
Doubtful.
The ceremony's tomorrow.
I won't push it back.
But, how will we...?
The new model won't be
making its debut.
We'll have to celebrate
ten years of peace
with a symbol of war.
[DIESE]
I expected nothing less
from the son
of Ledrad's late king.
His illegitimate son, if we're
being technical, your grace.
Right here.
Only royalty know about this.
Yes.
Most helpful.
[SERGE snoring]
[CHASE]
Let's say Hanns is responsible,
what would his motive be?
Well.
Maybe it was justice
for Eddy Lloyd.
He saw him being mistreated
and snapped.
It seems like
an awfully big risk.
Putting everything
on the line because
a co-worker was undervalued?
Jealousy?
Maybe involving the new model?
It was built by the Ministry
of Fairies
to symbolize unification.
Even if military mechanics
like Hanns are qualified
to be artificial
fairy technicians,
the Ministry doesn't
see them as equals.
And they didn't get to be
key figures in its development.
Maybe it left him bitter,
angry.
Which would explain
why he was determined
to shelve the Zern Ones.
If that was his only goal.
You don't buy it.
[CHASE] I'd like to look
into Eddy's personal life again.
I'm sorry.
I know we're busy.
Get the director's
permission first.
We'll be fine.
Thanks.
[sighs]
Just one more day
till the anniversary.
Then we can take a break.
[SERGE moaning]
[FREE] You can sleep
after tomorrow! Get up!
Ahhh! Take cover!
Are we under attack?
God help us.
One more day, huh?
Looks like you're back
in action.
♪
Oh, you're talking about Eddy?
I heard the guy forfeited
his whole pension.
Even though he had a son
to look after.
-[CHASE] A son?
-Sure.
Everybody knew how much
of a workaholic 'ol Eddy was.
Got to a point where his wife
was so sick of him,
she took off and decided
to raise the boy by herself.
His military record
never mentioned that.
[OLD MAN] Well, He definitely
brought him to work
a couple of times.
We'd play around with the kid
during our breaks.
[CHASE]
Eddy Lloyd had a son.
[fireworks popping]
There's something I've been
wondering about.
It's Chase.
His first name's Robert.
So how come no one
ever calls him that?
[FREE] You know what
the military police are?
[MARLYA]
Um, I've heard of them at least.
They're basically internal
affairs for the military.
He was with them in Cidal.
After the war was over,
he was assigned to keep
a close eye on soldiers
for the Security Bureau.
Then joined us.
It's not as if he's a bad guy,
but people don't trust
Military Police
or members of the Bureau
for that matter.
Next time, maybe I should try
calling him Robert instead.
I think he'd appreciate that.
[MARLYA chuckles]
[fireworks popping]
[knocking]
You think you could
knock any louder?
[CHASE]
Sorry.
Are you're Eddy Lloyd's wife?
My apologies.
His ex-wife.
No-good bastard.
I'm not here about him.
I'm actually looking for
information regarding your son.
[fanfare]
I found Ted Livingston.
He was raised by his mother
so his surname is different.
You introduced him
as your right-hand man.
Thing is, you never said
he was Eddy's son.
And so what if he is?
You were covering
for him all along.
Protecting him.
So nobody would find out.
Doing a favor
for your old colleague.
You need to get your head
out of the sand!
Think about it, Hanns!
If his son really is
the mastermind here,
you think whatever he's planning
stops with just the new models?
He's got something bigger
in the works!
[sighs]
He may.
There's a possibility
Ted might use
the Psyden Seven's
override function.
Override function?
What do you mean?
[CHASE]
Will I make it?
[HANNS]
I remember back in the day
when Eddy's son was just
a little kid running around.
Still, it took a while for me
to realize the new trainee
was the same boy
from all those years ago.
And it's not like his father
went out of his way to tell me.
Even after the war,
when Eddy quit
and disappeared
off the face of the earth,
Ted continued to devote himself
tirelessly to his work.
I'm sure he must've
been concerned
about his father's fate,
but he never even let on once.
[SOLDIERS]
Huh? What?
[CROWD chanting]
[HANNS]
Like the rest of us,
he wasn't involved
in the new model's development.
But if he used some
illegal instrument
to disrupt the device,
he could cause a breakdown.
The old artificial fairy model
Eddy developed
has a built-in
override function.
A disabled mode used
for test purposes.
And what happens
if he activates it?
What could he do then?
Operate them
all at the same time.
At least any number
of Psyden Sevens
within audible range of the
special override pipe he's got.
They'd ignore their operators?
That's why the function
was shut off.
He'd have to perform some
modifications to the frame.
Eddy was the only person who
knew how it was done, I thought.
The Arcame Mafia sheltered him
at one point.
We know they're in the city
and plotting something huge.
Can you imagine what'll happen
if Ted figured out
how to override
the older models?
I'm sorry, I believed
I was close to the boy,
but I never once suspected
he could be tampering
with the Zern Ones,
or that rage was boiling in him.
I failed Ted!
He was like a son to me!
Go, please!
Before it's too late!
Stop him from doing
something terrible!
[CROWD chanting]
[chanting continues]
[MARLYA]
Ray Dawn's here.
Meaning Ver's probably
in the crowd.
I don't think now's the
opportune time for you to act.
Yes, I agree.
I don't want it
to end too easily.
♪
-[FREE] Chase?
-What's the matter?
[CHASE]
It's the Psyden Sevens!
Calm yourself.
What about them?
There's no time!
We need to apprehend
Ted Livingston now!
You mean Hanns' assistant?
Find and arrest him!
[FREE]
At once, ma'am!
-Where's Ted?
-Not here.
He joined the crowd.
[CROWD cheers]
[TED]
Go ahead, Golbarn Helwise.
Talk about Unification.
Spread your lies.
All you did was eradicate those
who wouldn't obey you.
As soon as those
who followed you
and spent their lives working
to end the war became obstacles,
you made sure they were
"removed."
Like my old man!
[GOLBARN] As I look out on
the faces in the crowd, I see...
Huh?
[TED whistling]
A fitting end.
Killed by the artificial fairies
he designed to help you
win your war.
Prime Minister!
[CROWD shouting]
Idiot! [whistling]
You've done enough
for today, pal!
[TED grunting]
The pipe!
Look out!
Should've dropped it!
Are you all right, Excellency?
Shaken, but still alive.
The Prime Minister.
Someone tried assassinating him.
[VERONICA] And yet Ray Dawn
didn't even raise a finger.
Get in.
You're nothing
but Golbarn's dogs!
Probably never once had
an independent
thought in your life!
Far too busy serving
your overlord!
Are you done?
For a man of your conviction,
that was certainly
an undignified act, Livingston.
Undignified?
My father came up with those
artificial fairies,
and what'd he get?
His honor,
his dignity stripped away,
and the Security Bureau
endlessly hounding him!
Golbarn might've used
bureaucracy instead of a knife.
It's still murder!
Maybe you can't forgive him,
but accept this fact:
the war ended long ago.
And murderers are judged
fairly these days.
It's a good era.
So what?
You're saying Golbarn's a man?
Yeah.
He's a human.
The same as you.
That's why we refuse
to let you kill him.
[car engine starts]
[car driving away]
Well, I earned my pay.
Great job everyone.
That was good work
out there today, Robert.
Hmm? Oh, thanks.
Same to you.
Good night, Ozz.
And you too.
See you tomorrow!
Feels like this place
has changed
ever since she joined our ranks.
Huh, Robert?
[sighs]
Appears so.
[MARLYA] I've spotted
around 10-15 enemies!
-[BEEVEE] Then prove it!
-[FREE] Fairy's natural enemies.
[BEEVEE] You don't have what
it takes to fire me up.
The mediocre
should learn from defeat.