[gunfire]
The antiquated history
you worship
will be rewritten by my hand!
[roars]
[yells]
♪
It’s time for the curtain
to be raised at last!
No. It’s impossible.
No one has ever broken
through the Heavenly Gate.
Sir! What are your orders?
We need to halt
the enemy’s incursion
before they reach
the palace.
I-- Right!
Drive back this
rebel scum, men!
No. Kill every last one of them!
[GARRISON LEADER]
Yes, sir!
You won’t
survive the night, Liscar!
♪
Are you trying to follow
in my footsteps, Diese?
A foolish endeavor.
Pardon, where
are you going, sir?
Into the battle to deal
with this myself.
I’ve never been much
for waiting on others.
[MARLYA gasps]
They managed to breach
the Heavenly Gate!
-What now, sir?
-[FREE growls]
We stop Beevee Liscar.
Let’s move out!
[FREE grunts]
[gunfire]
[metal scraping]
-[SOLDIERS gasping]
-What have we here?
A pile of rubble!
[SOLDIERS groaning]
You’re dust!
Meant to scatter!
[SOLDIERS inhales sharply]
-[squelching]
-[heavy thud]
You lacked resolve.
Why bother standing
on the battlefield?
Weakling.
All this violence.
For what?
It’s unreal.
Only a small detachment
did this much damage?
Nothing about this
is surprising.
We’re dealing with a Fairy
Soldier, a genuine warrior.
You’re genuine, sir.
You also fought
in the War of Unification.
That’s right, I served.
With the director gone,
I’ll have to stop Liscar.
-[objects clatter]
-[FREE gasps]
Ah! Dorothea! Perfect.
Allies. It’s about time!
Military Minister Bohme?
Quickly! You can team-up
with us under my command.
We can outmaneuver them
but we must go now, hurry!
It’s your call.
Are you sure
we want to listen
to this guy’s strategy?
All right.
Several years ago,
back in 481 U.E.
Golbarn was the king of Cidal.
The emperor gave
an imperial command
for the king
to assemble his forces
and launch an invasion
into neighboring Timoon.
At that time,
nobody could’ve predicted
Cidal would
achieve unification.
It was unimaginable.
I was only a child
at the time.
True. Twenty-four years
is quite a while.
I was already serving
in the Ainedern military.
Attacking Timoon,
it seemed more insane
than reckless.
You could hardly
blame me for thinking
the order was falsified.
However...
[WOLF] According to history,
Garlan Battle,
the famed
Knight of Cidal,
was tasked
with removing the emperor
from the imperial capital
of Mazria.
At the time, it was under
the Kingdom of Ledrad’s control.
Everything changed
after that incident.
[DIESE]
Indeed.
The power structure
was built around two aspects:
Ledrad’s manipulation
of the emperor,
and my native Ainedern
acting as their accomplice.
Power structure.
Meaning what?
Conflict used to be
never-ending.
Though one truth
remained constant.
Ledrad and Ainedern’s supremacy
was never in question.
[WOLF]
I see.
But Golbarn was able
to overturn that framework
by obtaining a crucial
playing piece:
the emperor.
Golbarn’s a shrewd,
calculating man.
I was convinced that
after Unification
he’d find some way to install
himself as the new emperor.
[WOLF] And yet, he remained
a loyal subject.
[DIESE scoffs]
You’re a fool
if you think that.
It was fear.
The fear of forever
being branded a usurper.
[heavy thud]
Eizenkopf! Crush these pebbles!
[EIZENKOPF grunting]
Men! Stand your ground for
His Imperial Majesty--
Smells like death.
[EIZENKOPF snarling]
Peace rots a soldier
from the inside out,
and this place stinks of it.
[roaring continues]
[MAN grunts]
[grunts] Reinforcements!
We’re falling back for now!
-[MAN grunts]
-[stone shifting]
I never knew
these passages existed.
You’ll find the royal palace
is home to many secrets.
And there’s no single person
that’s aware of all of them.
[EIZENKOPF roaring]
They’re right below us.
[BOHME]
Exactly as I predicted.
This way we can get
the drop on them.
[chuckling]
Minister Bohme!
-News, soldier?
-Sir! Word from the West Gate!
Reinforcements have arrived
and are joining the fight!
Excellent! And who’s
their commanding officer?
[MESSENGER]
Actually...
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Did you think I’d stand by
and do nothing?
It’s my responsibility
to defend Rondacia,
and I’ll be damned
if I let some pack of rebels
turn it into their war zone.
[SOLDIER A]
Don't stop firing!
[SOLDIER B] Keep putting
the pressure on them!
Guess no one
told these idiots
their ammunition
will eventually run out.
[BEEVEE]
Just like old days.
Used to be like this
all the time
during the War of Unification...
before everyone went soft.
Feeling nostalgic, sir?
I live and breathe for this.
[DIPPER scoffs]
[gunfire ceases]
[BEEVEE]
That’s my cue.
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[laughs sinisterly]
[EIZENKOPF roaring]
Hold fast! We’re not
moving from this spot
until he’s dead on the floor!
[BEEVEE]
Here’s your chance.
Fight me.
I’m right here.
Don’t hold back.
♪
[EIZENKOPF grunts]
I’m waiting!
Prove to me
you’re more than just dirt!
Take this mad man down!
You can either run
or stand your ground.
Where you die
is entirely up to you.
Follow behind the colonel!
[MARLYA]
I don’t understand it.
Why do people fight?
What could be worth
all this bloodshed?
I can’t think
of a single thing.
War brings death.
But no one wants to die.
[MARLYA panting]
[footsteps approaching]
Looks like Free and the others
haven’t started,
so just hang tight.
[MARLYA chuckles softly]
This is where we part ways.
I’ll be seeing you soon.
[OZZ screams]
[MARLYA]
No.
I’m not
running away anymore.
This Liscar guy has to pay
for what he did!
Time to go.
-Minister!
-[BOHME] Hmm?
I was about to.
Forward, men!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[shouting continues in distance]
Oh.
Sounds like
we’re gonna have company.
Open fire!
[gunfire continues in distance]
[FREE]
Ozz.
I’m not going to ask you
to help me out here.
Just watch,
wherever you are!
I’ve been waiting for this.
-[metal scraping]
-[MEN grunting]
-Better than last time.
-You don’t say?
[BEEVEE laughs mockingly]
[FREE grunting]
[blades humming]
[BEEVEE chuckles]
Well done!
That’s more like it!
I don’t need your praise.
I’ll cut you down to size.
He’s on par with the colonel.
[gunshot]
If we don’t stop them,
the fighting will never end!
Sir, look out! From the rear!
-Wake up and face reality!
-[metal scraping]
This isn’t the age
of war anymore!
Nobody wants this but you!
[BEEVEE scoffs]
[BEEVEE]
Doesn’t matter what age it is.
[power hums]
Times change, but I don’t!
[roars]
Look, Free. See that?
When you’re overcome with fear
and lose sight of the goal,
that’s your destination.
Move forward.
[FREE] I will, Jet.
Thank you.
-[EIZENKOPF roars]
-[metallic scraping]
[FREE grunts]
-[energy humming]
-[FREE grunting]
♪
[BEEVEE scoffs]
[SOPHIE] Follow the colonel.
He’s heading outside!
[inhales sharply]
[snarls]
[RED HOOD snarls]
[roaring]
[groans]
Yes! More!
Keep going!
This is what
I’ve been waiting for!
You almost remind me
of the man
who originally held that sword,
like I was dueling
Jet Grave again!
You talk too much!
[EIZENKOPF roars]
You’re close,
but not there.
What? You think I don’t
already know that?
[EIZENKOPF snarls]
[EIZENKOPF roaring]
I’m not alone.
My goal was never
to beat you one-on-one.
[MARLYA]
Can you hear me, Ozz?
Your comrades will avenge you!
[groans]
Told you we’d meet again!
Look out!
We fight as one,
because we’re Dorothea!
[footsteps echoing]
[DIESE]
It won’t be much longer.
[WOLF] I’m surprised Christopher
Rahn pledged allegiance.
The man’s a surviving
Ledrad royal after all.
[DIESE scoffs]
Thanks to him,
I procured
the blueprints to the palace.
Make no mistake.
He’s not my only collaborator.
[WOLF] There are many
who support you,
and the reform
you’ll bring to the world.
Correct.
Once this is done,
and we’ve removed the emperor,
the opposing forces
feigning loyalty to Golbarn
will begin defecting en masse.
After they pledge fealty,
Unified Zesskia
will lose its support.
[WOLF]
You’ve worked it all out.
-[keys jingling]
-[door unlocking]
♪
[FREE grunts]
Don’t stop now.
I haven’t had a fight
this good in ages!
Stop treating it
like some kind of game!
[EIZENKOPF roars]
[FREE grunting]
[BOTH grunt]
[BEEVEE chuckles]
[BEEVEE grunts]
[inhales sharply]
This guy.
Looks like
we reached our limit.
Colonel! Come on!
Don't tell me
this will be our last time
fighting together. [grunts]
We’re finished here!
Make the call!
♪
[BEEVEE groans]
Enough for tonight!
[BOTH chuckle]
[KLARA gasps]
What is it?
Tell me, do you see something?
It’s the enemy.
They’re withdrawing!
[MARLYA hisses]
-[wind whistles]
-[coughing]
You won’t get away!
♪
[DIESE]
Hmm.
[GARRISON LEADER]
Who goes there?
I’ve come to demand an audience
with his Imperial Majesty.
You will grant me entrance
to the throne room immediately!
[GARRISON LEADER] It’s him!
Duke Hybranz!
You’re mistaken.
I am no longer a Duke.
My one true title is and
always will be Schwarz Diese!
You’re a traitor!
Guards!
[GARRISON LEADER groans]
[SOLDIERS gasping]
It’s imperative I see
His Majesty at once!
Don’t make me repeat myself!
[MARLYA panting]
Outta the way!
Marlya!
Where are you running to?
-[gunfire]
-[heavy thudding]
[CASTAL]
Tell me.
Why are you
disturbing my peace?
Why?
For your sake.
Isn’t that clear?
Hmm?
Where’s Wolfran run off to?
I could’ve sworn he was
following right behind us.
[RAY]
He performed his duty admirably
and had to depart.
[DIESE]
Hmm?
♪
Didn’t expect to see you.
Ray Dawn.
How’d you--?
Never mind. It’s obvious.
Wolfran’s been working
for you all along!
[RAY]
You know too much.
No good can come from that.
♪
[SOLDIERS gasping]
-It’s rust.
-It’s called Throne Taker.
That’s his fairy’s ability.
-[DIESE grunts]
-Hmm?
Unfortunately,
you have no understanding
of the times.
[SOLDIERS screaming]
What’s happening?
[loud boom]
[EIZENKOPF snarling]
[EIZENKOPF roars]
It can’t be.
Beevee Liscar is here?
All of you!
Protect the prime minister!
-[COMMANDER groans]
-[GOLBARN gasps]
[EIZENKOPF roars]
We can’t defeat them.
Retreat!
We’ll find another way inside!
[shuddering]
Why, Ray Dawn?
If you possessed such
tremendous power all along,
why stand by
as Golbarn’s sycophant?
Perhaps I should’ve
told you this sooner,
but I despise you.
Your shallowness
and cavalier attitude.
-Irritating qualities.
-[DIESE moaning]
You’ll be forever known
as Schwarz Diese, the traitor.
Not even death
will bring atonement.
History will never forgive those
who betray His Majesty,
the emperor.
[moans]
♪
Look at the carnage
they left behind.
Those guys really were trying
to start another war.
-[grunts] And they still can!
-[KLARA gasps]
-[FREE] Wait, Marlya!
-Let me go!
-He’s so close!
-And then what?
Is the only thing
you want revenge?
We drove the enemy forces
out of the palace.
The battle’s done.
We performed our duty.
[MARLYA inhales sharply]
And what about justice for...?
[crying]
Is victory enough for you?
It is.
[MARLYA breathes shakily]
So we really won today,
didn’t we?
We did.
They attacked, we fought back...
and won.
♪
[FREE] And just like that,
the war was over.
[WOLF]
What’s your reason for fighting?
What are you protecting?
[VERONICA] You can’t get back
what’s already lost!
[MARLYA]
Even if you get your revenge,
it won’t change the past!