[MARLYA] Twenty‐four
years ago in U.E. 481,
the War of Unification
seized Eastald.
Bloodshed and chaos quickly
spread throughout the land.
During this lengthy
and intense conflict,
weapons without equal
were employed...
[MARLYA]
...Fairy Soldiers.
[VILLAGERS murmur]
Why?
Ray Dawn? Why're you doing this?
Burn it all!
[VILLAGERS gasping]
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
[VERONICA]
People disagree. They fight.
Even if it costs
what's dear to them.
[VERONICA]
And all that's left
are actions that
can't be undone.
[MARLYA gasping]
[VERONICA]
Marlya.
[pants]
Uh?
Stand up. We have to go.
[MARLYA panting]
[FREE] The rain will
always stop eventually.
Everything has its end.
[MESSENGER A]
Attention! Official declaration!
We lost. It's over!
His majesty surrendered!
Attention! Official
declaration...
[FREE]
Damn it!
[FREE] But sometimes
the end comes too late.
[FREE] Nine years ago, with the
support from the king of Cidal,
Eastald was unified under
the emperor of Zesskia.
With that, the great conflict
came to an abrupt conclusion.
Although animosity
still existed,
and a litany of issues
were unresolved,
technically the War
of Unification was over.
On paper, at least.
[FREE]
You can't leave!
Stop, Wolf!
Wolfran!
[thunder rumbles]
[FREE] As for us Fairy Soldiers,
we were left with nowhere to go.
[trail whistle blows]
[MARLYA]
It's time to start over.
[FEMALE ATTENDEE A]
I'm looking forward to this.
[MALE ATTENDEE A]
Quite. Seems there's some
real treasure being
auctioned today.
[CROWD applauding]
[MALE ATTENDEE A] Better hurry.
Sounds like they're starting.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
I welcome you all.
Let me be the first to say
how truly grateful we are
you were able to join
us this evening.
What's truly astounding
is tonight marks our fifth,
that's right, fifth Squire
All‐Night Auction to date.
This wouldn't have been possible
if it hadn't been for you,
our patrons. Please accept my
most sincere gratitude.
Wait. Isn't this...
[FREE]
Hey. You, over there.
You're one of the Cocolu
Family's underlings?
So what reason do you
have to be back here?
Uh?
[FREE] Can't you hear the
auction's already started?
Get back to your post.
Yes sir, right away, sir!
Remind me, you're with
Gui Carlin, aren't you?
Head of security?
The name is Free.
And we've been
introduced before.
Yeah! Mister Free! That's right!
Drop the "mister."
Just "Free"‐‐I told
you that already.
[MARLYA]
Mm... I don't remember.
‐‐Y‐‐
‐‐[clattering]
I believe I did.
I suppose there's a chance
I wasn't listening.
Bottom line, none of you
guys are posted here.
So get back to work.
Right! Mister‐‐
Wait, I mean... Will do, Free!
[sighs]
Whatever.
Just hurry up and run along.
[MARLYA]
Yes, sir. Do you have any idea
what kind of creature
this is locked up in here?
[FREE]
Hey!
[AUCTIONEER A] Our next item
is something exquisite.
The centerpiece
of the first group.
Lot 23. Not only
a valuable investment,
but a piece rich with scientific
and historical importance.
A page taken from
the Black Fairy Tome!
[CROWD gasping, cheering]
Aww.
Adorable.
I told you to get back to work.
So stop handling
the merchandise.
[MARLYA]
My name isn't "you."
What?
[MARLYA]
I'm Marlya. Did you forget?
I introduced myself earlier.
You do remember.
Oh, sure. Sorry.
So, Marlya.
Why do you have a hunting rifle?
Because it's what I'm most
accustomed to using.
[gasps]
It's super‐friendly
around people.
Really, what kind
of animal is it?
[FREE] From what I understand,
unlike humans,
that thing is able
to see fairies.
Or, sniff 'em out,
it's one of the two.
I suppose you're gonna be
auctioned off as
well, little one.
[FREE]
You want to own it, no problem.
Just place the highest bid.
[MARLYA]
Mm...
Fairies.
[AUCTIONEER A]
One point five million galey!
I have 155! Do I hear...
I have two million galey!
[CROWD chattering]
Now that's one high‐quality
fairy bottle.
Notice how clearly you're able
to see the fairy primordials.
Wait, primordials?
What are those?
We're lookin' right at 'em.
[MARLYA] Mm. But they're
still fairies, right?
In a general sense.
I was using the formal
scientific term.
Over time, it's been shortened.
What we commonly refer
to as "fairies" are...
[inhales]
In any case, if they managed
to escape the bottle,
we'd never be able
to see them on our own.
How interesting. Good to know.
[gasps]
[MARLYA]
Well, aren't you clever‐‐ Uh!
I, uh, guess the cage
door must've come loose
somehow and the
creature escaped.
[FREE]
Escaped?!
Sure you didn't let
it out of there?
‐‐[CROWD screaming]
‐‐Uh. What is it now?
[GUARD A groaning]
[whimpering]
[GUARD A yelps, groans]
What is this?
[AUCTIONEER A]
You can't take that!
It's from the Black Fairy Tome!
[WOMAN]
And now it belongs to me.
You don't have any need for it.
[GUARD B] Who the hell
do you think you are?!
[GUARD B groaning]
There's no reason
to give my name.
[GUARD B groaning]
[screams]
[whimpering]
That woman's able
to use a fairy!
[FEMALE ATTENDEE C]
Everybody, run!
[MALE ATTENDEE D]
She'll kill us all!
I didn't expect this. A fairy?
[gasps]
[FREE grunts]
[FREE]
Get back here!
[FREE grunts]
[CROWD screaming]
Stop running!
[FREE grunts]
[FREE]
So that's her fairy?
I've never seen one
like it before.
[gasps]
[MARLYA]
I knew it. I finally found her.
Ver!
[VERONICA]
Uh?
Uh.
Is it really you?
Veronica!
[gasps] Marlya?
It's you.
I can't believe I found you.
Where have you been, Ver?
[clattering]
[FREE] Don't take your
eyes off your opponent!
Sorry to interrupt the
reunion, but for now,
you'll have to put it on hold.
Fancy moves for
only being a guard.
Honey, you're going to find out
why I'm head of security.
[FREE]
Dammit. This is a tough one.
I'm at a disadvantage like this.
What do you say we
even the odds a bit?
[roars]
[gasps]
[RED HOOD roars]
[MARLYA]
Both of you! Stop it!
[FREE]
And let her eviscerate me?
You don't want to do this!
Quit fighting!
Stay outta this!
[MARLYA]
Ver! Don't run away!
Hear me out!
[MARLYA]
Just hold on!
Where the hell do you
think you're going?!
You don't stand a
chance against her!
Look! Please don't follow me!
You'll only complicate things!
You're the one who's
complicating things!
[MARLYA]
Quit running! Ver!
Don't go!
Veronica from Suna
is gone forever.
Take my advice‐‐you should
forget about her.
Ver, no!
I was so close.
[CROWD screaming]
Stop! You could hit a guest!
Idiots...
[gunshots]
What's wrong with her?
[CROWD screaming]
Quick! This way! Hurry!
[GUARD E groaning]
[GUARD E]
Shit! Shit.
Shit!
[GUARD 01E grunting]
It's gonna break!
[MARLYA gasping]
A fairy.
She sees it?
[gasps]
[MARLYA]
Look out! Don't hit it!
This is where I'm from.
I'm back... in Suna...
Where we're both from.
That forest is now...
[MARLYA]
Ver...
[VILLAGERS murmur]
[MARLYA]
I don't understand.
Burn it all!
[GIRLS panting]
[MARLYA cries]
[VERONICA]
Ray Dawn. You were born in Suna.
It was your home,
and you destroyed it!
I swear...
I swear you'll pay for this!
Ver!
[screaming]
[CHIMA chirps]
You again.
What're you doing here?
Uh!
[MARLYA]
Uh.
Ver!
[RED HOOD growls]
[roaring]
[FREE panting]
[FREE growls]
[RED HOOD growls]
[BLOOD DAUGHTER growls]
A Fairy Soldier? You war relic.
[FREE]
And what about you?
How'd you manage to
get your hands on one?
Sorry, Veronica.
But you're too dangerous
for me to let you live.
I'm through holding back.
[FREE grunts]
Use your howl!
[RED HOOD growls]
[RED HOOD howls]
So, you were able to
withstand that, eh?
Doesn't matter.
[RED HOOD roars]
Stay where you are!
I will shoot you!
Do I need to remind you
that I'm with Gui Carlin?
Which means I'm your superior.
Oh, yeah? You don't say.
[FREE]
Hmph.
It's been so long,
but now I've found you.
Let's go, Veronica.
You thought joining the mafia
would help you find me?
That's right.
It was the quickest way
to track down your location.
But that doesn't matter.
Where have you been
all this time?
I missed you so much.
We're the only two survivors.
All that's left of our village.
But now we're together again.
That's enough.
[MARLYA]
Is something wrong, Ver?
And stop calling me that!
[MARLYA gasps]
Don't you listen?
The Veronica you knew
back then doesn't exist.
But I can see her right now.
You can't!
Not anymore.
[FREE grunts]
[RED HOOD roars]
[BLOOD DAUGHTER roars]
[RED HOOD growling]
I said stop it!
[MARLYA grunts]
[gasps]
[RED HOOD growls]
[gasps] She has one?
How, Marlya? You're like me?
[gasps]
[MARLYA]
Was that fairy mine?
But how?
What'd I do?
[gasps]
[MARLYA]
Where'd she go?
[CHIMA chirps]
[footsteps]
Do you have any idea
how difficult it was
infiltrating Gui Carlin?
Then you come along.
Infiltrate? So...
Are you saying you
were never a part
of their group to begin with?
You're affiliated with the
mafia. Heard of Dorothea?
The name should've come up.
They're an agency.
Government minions.
Charged with handling
illegal fairies.
[sighs]
It would've been better
if you hadn't seen her.
What do you mean?
That Veronica woman, who else?
She's able to use a fairy.
Additionally, she made off with
part of the Black Fairy Tome.
Which brings us to you.
[MARLYA]
I'm sorry?
You're able to control
a fairy as well.
Your very existence is illegal.
What happens now?
Are you going to arrest me?
[FREE] That's rather dire.
Maybe there's another way.
I'm with Dorothea,
in the First Unit.
Name's Free Underbar.
The question is,
should I arrest you,
or would rather become
a government dog?
Choice is up to you.
My name isn't "you."
It's Marlya Noel.
I wanna talk to Ver.
No matter what it might take.
[door creaks]
[footsteps]
And do you have it with you?
A shame.
Unfortunately, this page
happens to be a fake.
I can tell at a glance.
I see.
[door creaks, closes]
Marlya...
[MARLYA] It looks like the ruins
of some destroyed large city.
[NEIN]
A fairy primordial directly
possessing a human host.
[WOLF]
Weaklings like to swarm.
[KLARA]
They're a Fairy Soldier!
[WOLF] I see you still don't
know when to stop yapping.