[door slams]
[gasps]
Forgive the hour,
but we’ll be needing you
to come with us, Ambassador.
What’s the meaning of this?
Get him out of bed.
♪
[whistling]
I demand an explanation
at once!
You will be escorted
to the border,
at which point you will
permanently leave our country.
Your country?
-As in--?
-Correct.
As of now,
Hybranz is a sovereign state
and no longer a part
of Unified Zesskia.
What?
You’ve gone mad.
-[CHASE] Director!
-You both heard?
Yes ma’am.
There’s evidence of a revolt
taking place
in the Duchy of Hybranz.
Do you think it’s true?
What a dumb question.
It’s come to this,
Schwarz Diese.
You’ve betrayed us
after all.
[GOLBARN growling]
-[GOLBARN grunts]
-[glass shatters]
Damn that man!
If he was going to rebel,
why did he even bother saving
my life during the ceremony?
To get me to lower my guard?
You raise a good point.
Arcame was involved
in that particular incident.
If Duke Hybranz has connections
to their criminal
organization...
Of course he was involved!
Everything’s gone
according to his plan!
He pretended to have honor,
but it’s become apparent he’s
nothing more than a traitor!
Then again, the man has
a history of being a rebel.
[GOLBARN sighs]
Thing is, Diese wasn’t the only
one busy making preparations.
Military Minister Bohme.
Sir!
Within a few days, uh,
our forces...
You’ll have them mobilized
no later than two days from now.
[BOHME]
Understood.
Sir, by order of his Excellency,
in the event
the Duchy of Hybranz mutinied,
a strategy was drawn up.
However...
The plan relies heavily
on artificial fairies,
which is a problem.
They’ve been unreliable of late.
With regard to the Zern Ones,
the malfunction was due
to an interrupt device
installed by Ted Livingston.
As far as the older models
are concerned,
the override has been disabled
in ordinary frames.
Due to the limited number
that were produced,
all the new models
have been inspected.
They can be operated
with no problems.
But the Psyden Sevens
still need to be checked.
It’s brilliant.
We can’t use the old models
on the front lines
in case they’re overridden.
We’d lose the battle.
Which means we’re only safe
using the Zern Ones.
They really outwitted us.
Director Auler.
Sir.
[GOLBARN]
For extra insurance,
I’m requesting that you join
the suppressive force.
Additionally, I permit you
to retrieve the Fairy Weapon,
Aliadra.
Sir.
I’ll see that it’s removed
from the vault immediately,
prime minister.
What don’t these fools
understand?
Times have changed,
and all the world needs
is the emperor
symbolizing unification
and his people.
They’re trying to live
in the past.
Why, is beyond me.
[train whistle blows]
♪
Hmmm.
[BEEVEE whistling]
[CASTAL] So, Duke Hybranz
has staged a rebellion?
If memory serves,
we just rewarded him
for saving your life,
did we not?
It turns out he wasn’t
such a loyal subject
after all, Your Majesty.
[CASTAL] The complete opposite
of you, I trust.
Very well.
I proclaim on this day,
the traitor
and insurgent Schwartz Diese
is stripped of his
former title as Duke of Hybranz.
End this uprising, Golbarn.
Defeat him.
As you command.
♪
Director.
All for what?
Worthless ambition.
[MARLYA]
I don’t have to run.
No one’s ever told me
that before.
Maybe that’s all
I’ve been doing.
Fleeing.
Moving from one place
to the next.
But it’s not like
I wanted to keep running.
I only did it because
I had no other choice.
I couldn’t stay where I was.
See that?
Kinda weird, isn’t it?
Uh, mm-hmm.
[KLARA] No human needs that
many hours of sleep.
He isn’t normal.
I don’t know,
that’s taking it a bit far.
[SERGE giggling]
Okay--now that was weird.
Didn’t you just say.
Sure, but don’t tell me
that laugh wasn’t unsettling.
Admit it.
I find just about everything
he does to be highly suspicious.
Come on, Klara.
Maybe you’re being
too hard on him?
Just a bit?
[KLARA]
Honestly, no.
[FREE]
Are you serious?
A revolt led by Schwarz Diese?
What else do we know?
Details are still scarce,
but an imperial command
has been issued to quash it.
Well, that’s just great.
♪
The second we get back home,
we’re plunged into
the middle of a war.
It figures.
Let’s go!
Headquarters, now!
-[KLARA] Right.
-[MARLYA] Yes, Sir!
I was wondering
when you’d get back!
The director already left.
She departed yesterday
as part of the suppressive
force’s vanguard.
-Sorry you missed her.
-[CHIMA squeaks]
Wonderful.
[ELENOA] Chase and Lily’s
Third Unit went with her.
Wait, then the only Dorothea
left in Rondacia is us?
Yes, aside from support
personnel such as myself,
it’s just the four of you.
Coming back,
Duke Kal-o gave us a letter
we’re supposed to deliver.
-What should we do?
-If the director’s gone,
we’ll have to hand it
to the prime minister ourselves.
It can’t wait.
Who takes it?
[ELENOA]
Who’s senior here?
I’ll get back in the car again.
I wonder if we should
have gone with Free
to see the prime minister.
It’s not like he’s leaving
to go meet the enemy.
Plus he’s the director’s deputy,
and as far as rank goes,
I think he’s the only
one allowed in.
That’s true.
Oh well.
[CHIMA squeaks]
You’re worried about him?
I wouldn’t put it that way.
[SERGE]
Relax.
You may not know it
by looking at him,
but he gets the job done.
Every time.
He’ll be all right.
In short, he takes
his duties seriously.
Unlike some people we know.
[SERGE] Yeah?
Who’re you referring to?
[KLARA]
I think it’s obvious.
[SERGE]
No. Please.
Explain it to me.
We can’t blame ourselves
for tragedy.
We watch over each other.
Always.
[FREE] I know it’s
an unreasonable request.
Thank you,
Minister Bellwood.
[MARCO]
I don’t mind.
On the contrary,
I’m glad you came to me,
since you view this
as such an urgent matter.
I didn’t want to bother you,
but unlike the director,
I don’t have the clout
to see him right away.
Well, the prime minister
is terribly busy at the moment.
[GOLBARN] What’s this
pressing matter, then?
Allow me to present
the deputy commander
of Dorothea’s First Unit,
Free Underbar.
[FREE clears throat]
Your Excellency,
this is yours.
On our way back
from inspection,
Duke Kal-o gave us
custody of a letter.
Let me see that.
Here.
[gunshots]
[bullets ricocheting]
[explosion]
[blade slinging]
[metal crashing]
Move aside.
[SOLDIER]
Ah!
[gunshots]
[GOLBARN sighing]
[MARCO]
What word from Kal-o?
It’s a warning.
Appears Ray Dawn was able
to predict Diese’s insurrection.
Whatever source he’s using,
seems their information
is highly reliable.
We might’ve been able
to prevent the rebellion.
It’s a shame the letter
didn’t arrive here sooner.
That’s not all he writes of.
[canons firing]
All of a sudden we’re fighting
in the streets?
[LILY] The enemy’s weaker
than we thought.
Doesn’t that bother you?
I’m more concerned with
where Director Auler ran off to.
Don’t worry.
She’ll be just fine.
She’s one of the Seven.
[metal clanging]
[LILY]
The Witch of Ainedern.
[SOLDIER groans]
If you value your lives,
surrender now!
[SOLDIER yelps]
I was expecting them
to resist more than this.
[BEEVEE whistling]
-[SOLDIER] Hey, you there!
-[gunshot]
[whistling continues]
♪
[MARCO] You say there’s more
to the letter?
According to Duke Kal-o,
the buildup of troops
in the Duchy of Hybranz
merely served
as a diversion.
He wanted the Unified Forces
in his territory?
But for what purpose?
[GOLBARN] It’s difficult
to take at face value,
but the letter says...
Forgive the interruption,
Your Excellency!
-We just received word!
-[GOLBARN] Hmm?
[BUTLER]
The palace!
It’s under attack
by the enemy!
Sir, his Imperial Majesty
is inside!
[explosions]
♪
[guns firing]
[SOLDIER] Get in there!
Move it!
♪
[guns firing]
[gunshot]
♪
What is it?
They’re laying siege
to the palace.
The palace.
What?
Follow me, we’re moving out!
[ALL] Yes, sir!
Understood!
[bullets ricocheting]
[breathing shakily]
Whose artificial fairies?
Those don’t belong
to the Unified Forces!
Destroy them!
[guns firing]
[BOHME]
In the end, they’re just a mob.
Right. We’ll make our way into
the palace from this position.
Once inside, I’ll take command
and protect
His Imperial Majesty.
This day will go down
in the books, soldiers!
[FREE]
The palace has three gates.
The East Gate is near
East End Base.
-Second is the Heavenly Gate.
-It stays closed
except for special occasions
like ceremonies.
Security will be tight.
Which only leaves...
The West Gate.
That’s my bet.
Step on the gas.
♪
[BEEVEE whistling]
-[SOLDIER] Fire!
-[gunshot]
[guns firing]
[whistling continues]
What the hell happened?
Not one shot missed!
[BEEVEE whistling]
[DIESE] It pains me to think
about all those
we had to leave behind
in Hybranz.
Arcame will continue taking part
in the uprising
until it’s concluded.
Then expect to be rewarded.
Unlike Unified Zesskia,
I have no intention of imposing
a strict monopoly on fairies.
[WOLF]
If I’m hearing you right,
you’re talking
about free and open use.
It’s necessary.
Without change to stimulate
development,
we stay closed off
to the new world.
Some call that radical.
I call it ambitious.
[MARLYA] A fire!
The West Gate is burning!
[gunshots]
[MARLYA]
And there’s gunfire!
They don’t waste time.
Nice of them to attack
the capital.
I don’t believe this.
That’s strange.
Why aren’t we seeing
more troops in this area?
Enemies!
[whistle blows]
[guns firing]
[explosions]
[gunshots]
Not like I was expecting guns
to be effective.
♪
Wow, Jet!
Free, if something
were ever to happen to me,
I’d want you to hold on to this.
-Got it?
-[FREE] Me?
Not like it’ll come to that,
but you gotta think ahead.
-[FREE grunting]
-[blade slinging]
[metal crashing]
-[SOLDIER gasps]
-[whistle blowing]
[SERGE]
Very kick ass, sir.
Wait.
I recognize that sword.
Yeah.
[KLARA]
The Fairy Weapon, Verosteal!
They gave you permission
to take it out.
These look like Arcame’s
artificial fairies.
[FREE]
Let’s go!
[ALL] Yes, sir!
-[metal clanging]
-[explosion]
[SERGE] Must’ve used those
to set the gate on fire.
[KLARA] This isn’t how a regular
army engages in combat!
[guns firing]
Mercenary tactics.
Beevee Liscar’s nearby.
From the train.
[BEEVEE whistling]
[guns firing]
[whistling continues]
[rifles firing]
Move!
Go!
[BEEVEE whistling]
Colonel?
[whistling continues]
Any of you soldiers brave enough
to hit me with a slug?
Here’s the spot!
Someone’s sure to have good aim,
so pull the trigger!
[SOLDIER whimpers]
I’ve met pebbles with more
courage than you.
You’re grains of sand!
Enemy troops at East Gate
are nearly pushed back,
and our forces are superior
at the West Gate!
You’re dismissed.
Shall we relocate
our other units
and have them defend
the East Gate, sir?
With those numbers,
we could wipe out the enemy
in one fell swoop.
No. We’ll continue to bolster
our defense
while we have a separate unit
strike from behind.
Oh. Truly an excellent plan.
While they may have set me up
as Minister of the Military,
I put my time in
on the battlefield first.
Choosing to stay in the capital
instead of leading
the forces in Hybranz
seems to have been
divine providence!
I do have a reputation
for extreme luck.
-[door opens]
-[MESSENGER] Urgent report!
Sir.
Word from the Heavenly Gate.
A new enemy!
Stop panicking!
The Heavenly Gate wouldn’t yield
even if a force
of ten thousand marched on it!
[MESSENGER] You’re right, sir!
It’s just...
The approaching enemy
is one of the Seven Knights,
Beevee Liscar!
[BOHME gasps]
Liscar?
♪
[guns firing]
Let’s pursue.
[SERGE]
What a massacre.
How could those guys from before
be responsible?
Nothing about this is adding up.
Why did they fall back
right in the middle
of the attack on the West Gate?
The only logical explanation
is that it was a decoy!
If so, what’s their goal?
♪
[metal crashing]
[BOHME sighs]
It’s him all right.
That bastard.
[BOHME]
He’s taunting us.
What’re you fools waiting for?
Start shooting and don’t stop
‘til he’s riddled with holes!
[SOLDIER]
Yes, sir!
Open Fire!
The pinnacle of weakness.
I came all the way for this?
You don’t even deserve
the privilege of shooting at me.
Imbecile.
This castle has never fallen.
Not even during
the War of Unification.
No army has ever managed
to breach the Heavenly Gate.
You can’t argue against history!
[rifles firing]
Don’t get killed.
The antiquated history
you worship
will be rewritten
by my hand!
[roaring]
[BEEVEE yelling]
Goddamn you!
♪
It’s time for the curtain
to be raised at last!
♪
[BEEVEE] Fight!
Show them what you’re worth!
[RAY DAWN]
You don’t understand the times.
[MARLYA]
Is this all a game to you?
[WOLF]
The time has come.
[FREE]
We’re Dorothea.
And we’ll perform our duty!