♪
[GONZALEZ]
Nine years ago,
the War of Unification
came to an end.
Golbarn Helwise,
the king of Cidal,
surrendered his crown
to the emperor.
He became Prime Minister.
The following year,
Golbarn was officially
installed in the position.
In addition, five men who played
significant roles in the war
were granted territories,
along with titles
in the new government.
They were named
the Five Dukes.
However, this newly
established system
was not destined to last long.
Patrick Starry, Duke of Widonia,
was apprehended
as the ringleader of a plot
to assassinate
the prime minister.
Just before his trial,
he was poisoned and perished.
The Duke of Nova, Ewan Breeze.
So offended at being
suspected of rebellion,
he actually decided
to incite an insurrection.
This hero of the war, one of
the renowned Seven Knights,
was killed while fighting.
Umar Jujuman,
the Duke of Littroke.
Despite being a sworn friend
of Prime Minister Golbarn
during the war, his paranoia
ultimately proved stronger
and led him to stage a revolt.
He failed and was executed.
[gulping]
[GONZALEZ sighs]
They say the only way to attain
peace is through sacrifice.
Right.
[RYLAN]
It was a huge mistake.
They should have never
named those five Dukes
or given them any territory.
Of course they were
rewarded with titles
while the real heroes
on the front line
were completely overlooked.
[scoffs] I don’t know what
heroes you’re talking about.
-Can it, you old bastard!
-[MARLYA gasps]
You’re an old fart, same as me!
Say that again!
See what happens!
[RYLAN]
You’re the one who started it!
[MARLYA] You know what?
I think both of you are young!
-You mean it?
-Course she does!
Yep. Real children.
[sighing]
Only seven days left.
Then it’ll be ten years
since the war ended.
Seems like only
a distant memory now.
Almost a dream.
Then again...
Duke Littroke wasn’t
killed that long ago.
Just over a year.
So only two of em are left.
Shwarz Diese.
The Duke of Hybranz.
And Kal-O’s Duke.
Ray Dawn.
♪
[door opens]
Hmm. You’re looking well.
As are you.
[iron rattling]
[SERGE] All right, buddy.
In you go.
[SWINDLER grunts]
[SWINDLER] Hey, hey, hey!
Hold on a minute!
Look, is it so wrong for me
to try and earn
a little bread on the side?
When you try and make it seem
as though you own
a fairy primordial?
Yes, it’s very illegal.
[SWINDLER sighs]
Dammit!
Yow! Ah!
Exceptional quality
despite its age.
[metal clinking]
[CHASE]
Hmm.
It may just be an empty casing,
but if it is genuine,
then it’s illegal.
[CHASE] Excuse me.
A word, if I might.
[SHOPKEEPER]
D-Dorothea?
Hey, you’ve got the wrong idea!
That thing outside is, uh.
[MARLYA]
So those are the new models?
I’ve been seeing them a lot.
[FREE]
You mean the Zern Ones?
[MARLYA]
Improved artificial fairies.
They’re much different
than the older ones.
Their grand debut
is coming up soon.
They’ll be security at the
war anniversary ceremony.
But more preliminary testing
is needed before then.
You mean like a rehearsal
before the event?
[tones sounding]
[GIRL screams]
What the?
-[metal rattling]
-[GIRL whimpers]
No!
[whistles]
Damn! It’s not
listening to my commands!
♪
[tones sounding]
-Protect them!
-On it!
[OPERATOR] Why can’t I?
It’s malfunctioning!
Allow me!
Come on!
Activate the other two, quick!
[whistles]
♪
[tone sounding]
[OPERATOR panting]
[sighing]
-[GIRL crying]
-Everything’s all right, now.
Thank you for
saving my daughter!
[FREE] Were you able to pinpoint
the cause of the malfunction?
Greetings.
Dorothea, yes?
-Hello.
-You’re from the Ministry?
Correct. Griff Mercer.
You wouldn’t know it, but he’s
the assistant vice-minister.
Oh? So you’re
high ranking then.
I wish it was more glamorous,
but you’ll note
the “assistant” in my title.
I’m an errand boy.
[MECHANIC]
I heard you two were present
when this thing went berserk?
[FREE]
Yes, that’s correct.
I’m assuming you’re
with the military?
Just a civilian mechanic
under their employment.
You can call me Hanns.
And this one here is Ted.
My faithful right-hand man,
if you will.
[FREE] Hmm.
Hanns is head of
the Maintenance Division
and happens to be one of
the most exceptional
artificial fairy technicians
alive.
[HANNS chuckles] Compliments
will get you nowhere.
[GRIFF chuckles]
[sniffing]
[MARLYA]
So, what did you find?
[TED] Our inspection turned up
nothing unusual.
[GRIFF sighs]
To be straightforward,
I’m not sure my superiors
are going to accept that answer.
We were phasing out
the older Psyden
Seven models completely,
which have been in use
since the War of Unification.
And the brand new Zern Ones
were supposed to be
their replacement.
Well this is a headache.
-That’s an understatement.
-One other thing.
Huh?
[horse whinnies]
[NEIN] We received info
from a certain source
regarding the Black Fairy Tome.
When we were over
at East End Base,
Assistant
Vice-Minister Griff
mentioned there’d been
some sort of new development.
The timing couldn’t be better.
The one you obtained
in Isharot was a fake,
but this time,
it could be the real thing.
I’ll be sending Marlya
to retrieve it.
Just me?
Who’s my partner then?
There isn’t anything
to worry about.
She’s a pro.
♪
Oh wow.
[KLARA] I’ve never been
to this city before either.
[MARLYA]
Hopefully we don’t get lost.
We saw the map,
so I don’t see how we could.
[MARLYA groans]
[horse neighs]
[bar chatter]
[nervous laughter]
♪
I assume you’re Buz,
the informant
we’re supposed to meet?
[chuckles]
It is my understanding,
you’ve been well paid.
Whatever information you have,
let’s hear it.
About that, the advance payment
wasn’t enough.
You’ll need to sweeten
the deal somehow.
[MARLYA groans]
But if you little Dorothea
bitches prefer to fight.
[BUZ snaps]
[shouting]
[MAN groans]
♪
[grunting]
Ah!
[HENCHMAN]
Boss!
[BUZ breathing shakily]
[chuckles]
Relax!
Don’t you two know a joke
when you hear one?
Huh? Huh?
One more time.
Tell us what you know.
Sure.
My pleasure.
[CHASE]
Think hard.
You noticed nothing unusual
about the artificial fairy?
[OPERATOR sighs]
If there was,
I didn’t have a clue.
Thank you for your time.
Must be a defect.
Or somebody sabotaged it
without us knowing.
I doubt anyone on the outside
would be able to tamper
with a military-grade
artificial fairy.
-Huh?
-[FREE] Hmm?
Daniel?
A former colleague,
I take it, Chase?
Yeah. I think he’s still
assigned to the Security Bureau.
-Give me a minute, sir.
-Sure.
♪
Something keeps nagging
at me, but what is it?
I’m your loyal subject,
at your command!
Girls, whatever you need,
just name it!
That’s a switch.
Since you offered, we’ll need
a vehicle for two people.
No problem, boss!
It’s done! One sec.
Hey! You’re moving up, Boss.
[BUZ] There was an auction
recently held in the city.
It was there the actual Black
Fairy Tome was put up for sale.
They referred to it
as “The Black Four”
or something to that effect.
Most of the attendees were
bidding huge sums of money,
trying to win the prize.
But in the end, the highest
amount was from an agent
who’s no stranger
to these kinds of circles.
A man. Goes by the name Dice.
-Look. That the guy?
-[inhales sharply]
[KLARA]
Yes.
♪
-Hang on.
-Got it.
♪
-It’s about to leave!
-We’ll make it!
Dorothea.
-We’re in pursuit of a suspect.
-[ATTENDANT] Understood.
-Please go on through.
-Much appreciated.
Thank you.
[whistle blowing]
♪
-[whistle blowing]
-[groans]
-Hurry it up!
-[MAN gasps]
Or I’ll punch your ticket,
you get me?
We’re boarding!
-Official Dorothea business.
-Oh, yes, ma’am!
[horn blowing]
Train for Rondacia!
Now departing!
[horn continues]
Just a moment, madame,
I’m sorry.
-You want my ticket? Here!
-Your admission isn’t the issue.
[horn blowing]
[gasps]
I’m afraid the train’s
already left.
[SWEETIE growls]
Bitter Sweet, too.
It wasn’t just Dorothea.
Seems Gui Carlin also
had information pertaining
to the Black Four’s location.
♪
Nothing.
I could’ve sworn
he got on this train.
[horn blowing]
-Have any luck?
-Mm-mm.
Let’s check once more.
Right.
He doesn’t seem
to be on board.
We should check
the freight car too.
[KLARA] You can’t enter or exit
while we’re in motion.
Isn’t the train’s next stop
coming up at a station
called Sharbit?
[KLARA] When we arrive, let's
have the attendant open it.
We’ll check the interior then.
[MARLYA] So, Klara, this is
the first mission
I’ve gone on where
it’s just been you and me.
I’m curious.
How did you end up in Dorothea?
I joined willingly.
♪
[KLARA] My entire family
was lost in the war.
[breathing shakily]
-[NEIN] That's far enough!
-[SOLDIER] Huh?
[MEN grunting]
[gasps]
[KLARA] Then she came along.
Director Nein.
She saved my life.
♪
[laughs softly]
[chuckles]
It hasn’t been easy for you.
The war destroyed
many people’s lives.
Both my parents.
They died before
I got the chance
to know either one of them.
[KLARA] In that case,
I guess that makes me fortunate.
[MARLYA gasps]
I’m grateful.
Even though
I lost mine, too,
at least I have memories.
♪
[cries softly]
[horn blowing]
Are you getting off
at the next station?
[MAN chuckles]
Ha!
You made his day, mister.
[brakes screeching, hissing]
-[KLARA] Sharbit Station!
-[MARLYA] Let’s hurry!
[KLARA]
If you would.
-He’s not here.
-How’d we miss him?
The briefcase!
♪
-Don’t let that man get away!
-[MAN] Huh?
Let’s split up!
Stop right there!
He’s gone.
♪
-[metal clicks]
-[gasps]
You’re coming with us.
Hands up in the air.
[chuckles]
Seriously? How long are you
going to keep this up?
-Anything?
-He’s stonewalling us.
Even if we tried getting him to
talk by breaking a limb or two,
I doubt it would
make a difference.
[KLARA]
He didn’t have anything
resembling the Black Fairy
Tome on him.
But he’s supposed to be the one
who won it at the auction.
If he’s acting as an agent,
he must’ve been bidding
on someone else’s behalf.
Whoever it is, I doubt he’s
going to open up about it.
[SERGE] There you are!
-I missed you, Klara!
-[KLARA groans]
So how’d the mission go?
I bet you were
lonely without me.
-It was quieter.
-Aw! I missed you too!
[MARLYA]
That malfunctioning Zern One,
did they find out
what’s wrong with it?
[FREE] We haven’t discovered
anything out of the ordinary.
[MARLYA] And Dice isn’t
cooperating with us.
What next?
[chuckling]
-Axel? You!
-Hold it right there!
[hissing]
[AXEL]
Everyone! Take it down a notch!
-[AXEL groaning]
-Oh. Right.
I almost forgot--you were shot.
And I nearly died, too.
I tell you,
that woman’s cold-blooded.
Shooting me in the back!
-I’m surprised you’re alive.
-[AXEL chuckles]
I still manage to get around,
especially when I need
to see my good friends.
-Uh-huh.
-That last time?
I had no idea
you were going to be there.
Blind luck.
It could happen to anyone.
So what do you say?
No hard feelings?
[FREE] Whatever.
I’ve got a full plate right now.
With the anniversary
of the war coming up, right?
I’m sure you’re prepared.
But if you need any help at all,
be sure to let ‘ol Axel know.
Then again, you do know
an awful lot of people
and have a habit
of hearing too much.
[AXEL]
Well, well. Dice.
Do you know him?
[AXEL] He’s famous.
In certain circles.
A real professional
who doesn’t talk much.
Who employs him?
[AXEL] It’s rare for an agent
of his caliber to be hired
by only a single client.
But, according to rumor,
Dice usually
works for one man.
♪
Gilbert Warlock.
We need to chat.
[BOHME] Thank you for the meal,
but if you’ll excuse me,
Duke Diese,
I must be on my way.
But, Military Minister,
you’ve only arrived.
Why not stay a little
while longer?
I’m afraid that’s out
of the question.
[DIESE]
I hope it’s nothing serious.
You must keep this between us.
The fact is...
there’s been a malfunction
with a Zern One model.
Oh!
What terrible news.
[HANNS] Look at the state
this Zern is in.
[CHASE] It's painful,
suspecting someone close.
[WOLF]
Don’t worry.
[SWEETIE] They're standing
right here. This is my present.
[NEIN]
Ears within Gui Carlin, eh?