- Yuto: IN THE CITY
WHERE WE LIVE,
THERE ARE TWO KINDS OF PEOPLE.
THE FIRST, ARE NATIVES,
PEOPLE WHOSE BODIES
ARE WHOLLY ORGANIC,
FREE OF MECHANICAL ALTERATION.
OTHERS ARE CALLED RESEMBLE,
PEOPLE FITTED WITH
CYBERNETIC PARTS,
WHICH COMPLEMENT
THEIR BODILY FUNCTIONS,
OR GREATLY ENHANCE
THEIR CAPABILITIES.
NOW, A THIRD CATEGORY
HAS EMERGED.
A TOTALLY NEW TYPE OF BEING,
ONE THAT IS 100% CYBERNETIC,
A TECHNOLOGICAL MARVEL LONG
DREAMED OF BY MODERN SCIENTISTS,
BUT WHICH MANY BELIEVED
TO BE IMPOSSIBLE.
THE DREAM, HOWEVER,
HAS SOMEHOW BECOME A REALITY,
AND FITTINGLY, IT HAS BEEN
GIVEN A NAME, GENUINE.
HAVING SAID THAT,
THIS HAS ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS STORY.
- ( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
- ( alarms sounding )
- TIME FOR PLAN B.
GUESS I'LL HAVE TO HIDE IT
OVER THERE FOR NOW.
- OH, WOW! WOULD YOU LOOK
AT THE SIZE OF THIS BATHTUB.
- FOR THE FIFTIETH TIME,
IT'S AN INDOOR POOL.
- I CAN'T THINK OF A NICER
WAY TO SPEND A DAY OFF
THAN AT A PLACE LIKE THIS.
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WHAT ON EARTH ARE YOU
DOING HERE, SILVIA?
- ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
WAIT AROUND 'TIL THEY CLOSE,
THEN THE PRIZE'LL BE ALL MINE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- SOLTY! C'MON AND PLAY.
- ( gulping )
- ( exclaims ) UH, SOLTY?
- HEY, WILL SHE...
- NO. SHE'S PERFECTLY SAFE.
THERE'S NO CHANCE
SHE'LL RUST OR STAIN.
RESEMBLE TECHNOLOGY'S
COMPLETELY WATERPROOF.
- BUT IT'S HER FIRST TIME.
I WONDER IF WE SHOULD'VE
PUT HER IN THAT
RESEMBLE SWIMMING WORKSHOP?
- TRUE, BUT SHE'LL BE FINE.
- GOOD AFTERNOON!
WOULD YOU LIKE TO
ORDER ANYTHING ELSE?
I MUST ADMIT I DIDN'T
EXPECT TO SEE YOU HERE.
- Roy: YEAH, WHATEVER.
- Yuto: ROY, DO YOU KNOW
THIS GIRL?
- NOT A CLUE. PROBABLY FISHING
FOR A BETTER TIP OR SOMETHING.
- ( scoffs ) YOU'VE GOT
SOME NERVE.
- OKAY, I'D LIKE TO
PLACE AN ORDER.
- I CAN PUT UP WITH A LOT,
BUT THE ONE THING
I ABSOLUTELY CANNOT STAND
IS TO BE TOTALLY IGNORED.
- AM I MISSING SOMETHING?
- NO, BUT SHE IS.
- DON'T EVEN PLAY DUMB WITH ME.
- WRONG TABLE, SWEETHEART.
- YEAH, RIGHT, I KNOW THAT
YOU'RE HERE WITH SOLTY.
STILL FEEL LIKE PLAYING
GAMES NOW, HUH?
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, I'M OKAY.
- ( sighs ) SOMEBODY
ORDER SOMETHING.
- LET ME SEE HERE.
I'D LIKE A COCONUT COCKTAIL.
- YEAH, OKAY.
ONE COCONUT JUICE THING AND...
I JUST HAVE TO SAY
ONE THING TO YOU, JERK.
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
INTERFERING WITH MY WORK.
YOU GOT THAT?
- INTERFERE WITH WHAT?
WAITING TABLES?
- WAFFLE ON ONE.
- YOU FINISHED?
- YEP, I THINK THAT'LL
ABOUT DO IT.
- HOW'D YOU GET IN?
- AS YOUR GUEST, OF COURSE.
- OH, YOU'RE GIVING ME
A HEADACHE.
- OH, STOP GETTING
SO WORKED UP.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE
REALLY OUT ANYTHING.
AFTER ALL, YOU DID
WIN THE TICKETS.
- WAIT, HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
- WELL, YOU HAD FOUR TICKETS,
IT WOULD'VE BEEN AN AWFUL SHAME
IF YOU LET THEM GO TO WASTE.
- LEARN TO SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
- ( groaning )
- STOP IT.
YOU'RE HURTING ME.
- ( sighs ) A DAY OF R AND R
IS JUST WHAT THE DOCTOR ORDERED.
TOO BAD INTEGRA HAD
TO WORK TODAY.
- ( sighs )
UGH, I REALLY NEED
TO GET A LIFE.
- ( phone ringing )
- HELLO?
SPECIAL SECURITY SECTION 7.
HMM?
( gasps )
- OH, WHATEVER.
I REALLY DON'T CARE IF
YOU GUYS ARE HERE OR NOT.
THERE'S NOTHING ANY OF YOU
CAN DO TO MUCK UP MISS ROSE'S
TOTALLY PERFECT CRIME.
- PERFECT CRIME?
YOU'RE ROSE ANDERSON?
- UH, YEAH. I AM!
- WHO GIVES A DAMN.
NOBODY HIRED ME TO PUT UP
WITH YOUR NONSENSE TODAY, KID.
SO, WHY DON'T YOU
JUST SCRAMBLE.
- SHUT UP.
AND DON'T FLATTER YOURSELF.
I'VE GOT BETTER THINGS TO DO
THAN KEEP YOU COMPANY, OLD MAN.
- HOLD IT. WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING WITH THAT?
- YOU CURIOUS?
- HARDLY.
- GOOD. I'LL TELL YOU.
- OOH.
- I'M SURPRISED HE
HASN'T GONE OFF.
THINK WE SHOULD WE WARN HER?
- NO, JUST DUCK.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT THERE
IN BLACK AND WHITE.
"AN EMERALD WORTH BILLIONS
STOLEN FROM THE
R.U.C. ART MUSEUM."
BUT THE BEST PART
ISN'T IN THE HEADLINES.
A SCOOP EVERY REPORTER
IN THIS CITY WOULD KILL
TO GET THEIR HANDS ON.
- Silvia: THE STOLEN EMERALD
IS HERE?
WHAT? ARE YOU CERTAIN?
- Integra: NO, BUT THERE IS
A HIGH PROBABILITY.
IT'S A LEVEL B ASSIGNMENT.
WE'VE BEEN ORDERED TO RECOVER
THE EMERALD AT ANY COST.
- BUT THIS WAS OUR FIRST
DAY OFF IN A LONG TIME.
- I UNDERSTAND, BUT THESE ARE
THE HAZARDS OF THE JOB.
NOW, STOP COMPLAINING
AND GET TO WORK. GOOD LUCK.
- IS THERE ANY OTHER...
- ( chuckles )
- YOU'RE NOT PULLING
OUR LEG, ARE YOU?
IT REALLY WAS YOU WHO
STOLE THE EMERALD LAST NIGHT?
- UH, WELL, DUH.
MISS ROSE, THE BRIGHT BLUE
METEOR OF HOPE STRIKES AGAIN.
- THE FACT THAT IT'S IN THE NEWS
PROVES THAT YOU FAILED.
I SEE A BRIGHT ORANGE JUMPSUIT
IN YOUR FUTURE.
- AND WHAT GOOD IS A STELLAR
PERFORMANCE WITHOUT COVERAGE?
THE STUPID NEWSPAPERS
HAVE DONE ME A FAVOR.
THEY'VE JUSTIFIED MY CAUSE.
I'M LIKE, THE PEOPLE'S NEW
CHAMPION, OR SOMETHING.
- OH YEAH, WE RECEIVED
A JOB REQUEST ON YOUR ROBBERY.
I THINK THAT WHOEVER
RECOVERS THE EMERALD
WILL RECEIVE A BOUNTY WORTH
TEN PERCENT OF ITS VALUE.
- TEN, HUH?
I'M PRETTY IMPRESSED.
- I'M NOT. IT'S PATHETIC.
WHAT ABOUT THE
WORTHINESS OF THE CAUSE?
IT'S LIKE ALL ABOUT
THE MONEY WITH YOU.
- JUST GO FOLD SOMETHING.
- SOME EGO. SHE CERTAINLY
HAS QUITE THE HIGH OPINION
OF HERSELF, DOESN'T SHE?
- WHAT GAVE YOU THAT IDEA?
- THE COLD FACT IS YOU'RE JUST
AN ORDINARY THIEF.
BET YOUR PARENTS
ARE REAL PROUD.
- SURE WERE.
ECSTATIC, ACTUALLY.
IN FACT MY MOM AND DAD
WERE CAREER THIEVES
UNTIL THEY RETIRED
A FEW YEARS AGO.
- HI, ROSE.
WAIT, ARE YOU ROSE?
- YEAH, AND WARNING,
STAY OUT OF THIS ONE.
- WHAT?
- ALL RIGHT. LOOK, I KNOW
HOW USEFUL YOU CAN BE.
I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN
YOUR LATEST PERFORMANCE.
- ( screaming )
- SOMEDAY, IF YOU EVER GET
TIRED OF YOUR OLD MAN,
I'LL TURN YOU INTO
A MASTER THIEF.
SEE YOU.
- NA-NA-NA-NA.
I AM SUPPOSED TO
BE OFF WORK TODAY.
- GROW UP, CELICA.
WE HAVE A THIEF TO CATCH.
- ( all gasping )
- HEY, DID YOU SEE HER?
- WASN'T THAT...
- OH, YOU'VE GOTTA BE MENTAL.
WHY ON EARTH ARE YOU
HIDING WITH ME?
- WELL, I...
- I NEVER EXPECTED
THEM TO SHOW UP.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING HERE?
- ARE THEY FRIENDS OF YOURS?
- THEY'RE FROM R.U.C. SECURITY.
SPECIAL TASK FORCE.
THEY WORK BEHIND THE SCENES,
MOSTLY-TRACKING DOWN ONLY
THE MOST NOTORIOUS CRIMINALS.
YOU MIGHT SAY THEY'RE
THE R.U.C.'S HUNTERS.
AND THEY'RE VERY GOOD
AT THEIR JOB.
- OH, YEAH?
- PERSONALLY, I'VE NEVER HAD
A RUN-IN WITH THEM.
BUT BELIEVE ME,
THEY'RE THE ENEMY, SOLTY.
AND THEY DON'T LIKE ME.
LUCKILY, I ALREADY HAVE
WHAT I CAME HERE FOR.
EVEN IF THEIR OBJECTIVE
WAS TO DISRUPT MY PLAN,
THEY'RE TOO LATE.
I'M HOME FREE...
( gasps )
- THAT'S ODD.
THERE'S NOTHING COMING OUT.
- OH, NO.
I TOOK THE WRONG ONE.
- WHAT? YOU WANTED SALT?
- ( gasps ) WHAT TO DO?
THINK, ROSE. THIS CAN'T
FALL APART NOW.
- UH, ROSE.
- DON'T BOTHER ME.
I'M BUSY NOW.
- WHY DO YOU DO
THINGS LIKE THIS,
THINGS THAT GET YOU
INTO TROUBLE?
WHY DO YOU HAVE
TO STEAL STUFF?
- ( rattling )
- WHAT THE HELL.
IT'S LIKE THERE'S SOMETHING
INSIDE BLOCKING THE HOLES.
AND IT'S RATTLING.
- COULD BE THE LOST EMERALD.
THAT'S WHERE I'D HIDE IT.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- TELL ME, SOLTY,
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
THE UNDERGROUND CITY?
- UM, NO, WHY?
- WELL, YOU'RE LUCKY.
IT'S A CESSPOOL OF
TRASH AND BILE,
UNFIT FOR RATS,
LET ALONE HUMANS.
YET THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE ARE FORCED
TO CALL THIS WASTELAND HOME,
BECAUSE THEY HAVE
NOWHERE ELSE TO GO.
LAW MAKERS CALL
THEM INCOMPENTERS,
UNREGISTERED CITIZENS.
AS SUCH, THEY HAVE
NO ACCESS TO JOBS,
HEALTH CARE, OR EVEN SCHOOLS.
THE GOVERNMENT CHOOSES TO
PRETEND THEY DON'T EXIST.
BUT THE TRUTH IS,
THEY'RE NORMAL PEOPLE
WHO'VE BEEN DEALT A ROTTEN HAND
BY THOSE WHO SHOULD'VE
PROTECTED THEM.
THE POLICE DON'T PATROL
DOWN THERE,
SO IT'S BECOME A HAVEN
FOR CRIMINALS.
THOSE WHO TRY
TO GET REGISTERED
ARE TURNED AWAY BECAUSE
OF A STRICT POLICY,
WHICH CALLS FOR APPLICANTS
TO PAY A STIFF FEE
AND ATTAIN A GUARANTOR.
DON'T THOSE STUPID JERKS KNOW
IF WE COULD AFFORD THOSE THINGS,
WE WOULDN'T BE
LIVING IN FILTH?
WEIGH THEIR SUFFERING
AGAINST THE TENS OF BILLIONS
THIS STONE'LL GO FOR AND
YOU'LL SEE HOW LUDICROUS
OUR SYSTEM IS.
THAT MONEY COULD BETTER
THE QUALITY OF LIFE
FOR ALL THOSE PEOPLE.
THAT IS WHY I STEAL.
BUT NOW, ALL HOPE IS LOST.
- I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- NO, WAIT. SOLTY.
- EXCUSE ME.
- HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
I KNOW YOU.
- I NEED YOU TO GIVE ME
THAT SHAKER THING.
- THIS ONE?
YES!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I NEED IT.
'CAUSE A LOT OF PEOPLE'S LIVES
DEPEND ON WHAT'S INSIDE.
- IDIOT.
- YOU'RE TELLING ME PEOPLE NEED
THE PEPPER IN THIS THING.
- THAT'S ODD.
- PLEASE.
- THIS IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN MY SALAD?
- YES.
- UH, ROY, SHOULDN'T
WE STOP HER?
- LET HER BE.
- LOOK, KID, THE GRINDER
BELONGS TO THIS CAFE.
IF YOU WERE TO TAKE IT,
THAT'S CALLED STEALING.
AT WHICH POINT,
ALL I COULD GIVE YOU IS A
RIDE TO THE POLICE STATION.
- I HAVE TO HAVE IT.
- PERSISTENT.
- PLEASE HELP ME.
I COULD SAVE SO MANY LIVES.
BUT I CAN'T DO THAT WITHOUT...
I NEED THE EMERALD
IN THAT SHAKER.
- ( grunting )
- YOU'RE...
YOU'RE ROSE ANDERSON.
- ( whistles )
- I'LL BE TAKING THIS ORDER
TO GO, IF YOU DON'T MIND.
- NO, YOU WON'T.
- ( screams )
- GET BACK HERE!
( grunting )
- IT'S YOU.
- I WILL NOT LET YOU STOP HER.
- COME TO MOMMA!
- HOPE THIS DOES THE TRICK.
- HUH?
( grunting )
- THIS IS OUT OF CONTROL.
ROY, WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
- TAKE A NAP.
- THEY'LL DESTROY
THE WHOLE COMPLEX.
MIRANDA MUST BE GOING OUT OF
HER MIND LOOKING FOR HELP.
- ( sighs )
I ALMOST FEEL GUILTY,
THE TWO OF US BEING IN
HERE AT A TIME LIKE THIS.
- DON'T EVEN SWEAT IT, MOM.
ROY SAID TO IGNORE THEM.
AND BESIDES KEEP YOUR MIND
ON THE PRIZE.
FIRST ONE TO LEAVE HERE
BUYS THE ICE CREAM.
- OKAY, OKAY.
- ( yelling )
- NO, NO. SHE IS NOT
GONNA MESS UP MY DAY OFF.
- THERE'S AN INCOMING MESSAGE
FROM HEADQUARTERS.
- EARPLUGS.
I CAN'T HEAR A THING.
- SEEMS THEY'RE
WILLING TO PAY A BONUS
TO WHOEVER RECOVERS
THE EMERALD FIRST.
- COME ON, LET'S GO.
THINK I'LL GET MY CHECK
BEFORE THE MALL CLOSES?
- WHAT PEOPLE DO FOR MONEY.
- ( screaming )
- I GOT IT!
STOP IT. THAT TICKLES.
LET GO.
( gasps )
- THINK AGAIN, GIRL.
- ( gasping )
- JUST A LITTLE FARTHER.
- NOT SO FAST.
- ( exclaims )
- SO LONG.
- ( screaming )
- LITTLE GIRL, IF YOU WANNA
SEE YOUR NEXT BIRTHDAY,
YOU'LL GIVE THAT TO ME
RIGHT NOW.
- HELP!
- IT'S ALL RIGHT NOW. NO ONE'S
GONNA HURT YOU. PROMISE.
- THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE
WHO NEED THAT MORE THAN US
SO WILL YOU HELP ME RETURN IT?
- ( giggles )
OKAY!
- Both: JUST LIKE THAT?
- ( in singsong tone )
I GOT IT. I GOT IT.
( chuckles )
BUT, NOW THAT I HAVE IT,
WHO SHOULD I TAKE IT TO?
- YOU DON'T HAVE IT. SEE?
( laughs )
( in singsong tone ) I GET
THE BONUS. I GET THE BONUS.
- NO, WAIT.
THAT CAN SAVE PEOPLE'S LIVES.
- WHAT IS IT WITH THIS
FREAKING GIRL? AXELA, CATCH.
- ( exclaims )
- HAND IT OVER!
- WHAT... WHO...
YOU TAKE IT.
- THAT'S MINE!
- NO, MINE!
- GIVE IT TO ME, NOW!
- YUTO, OVER HERE.
- SOLTY. I KNOW SHE'S
COMPLETELY CYBERNETIC.
YET, HER BODY LOOKS
HUMAN IN EVERY WAY.
NOT ONE SEAM.
JUST PURE, INNOCENT PERFECTION.
AUTONOMOUS AI!
AND ABOVE ALL, THERE'S HER
SWEET, UNASSUMING SMILE.
AM I... AM I IN LOVE?
HERE, SOLTY. I LOVE YOU. CATCH!
( exclaims )
I NEVER COULD PITCH.
- IDIOT.
- ( all gasping )
- Ringmaster: WELCOME TO THE
AMAZING WATER CIRCUS.
WE PROUDLY PRESENT THE
WORLD-FAMOUS TRAPEZE DUO,
THE GOLDEN FLYERS,
LAYLE OLAH AND FURIK VON SHITEN.
TONIGHT, THEY SOAR ABOVE
THE WATER, WITH NO NET.
- MOVE!
- ( exclaims ) SECURITY.
- PARDON ME.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- Both: I'LL GET IT THIS TIME!
- OH, GREAT.
- ( screaming )
- Both: GOT IT!
- THAT PRIZE MONEY'S MINE.
- CAREFUL, YOU'RE STRETCHING IT.
THAT'S MY FAVORITE SWIMSUIT.
- ( crowd cheering )
- HEY, WATCH IT, WILL YOU?
- SORRY. MY BAD.
- ( gasps )
- THIS TIME, NOTHING'LL STOP ME.
- WAIT.
- ( gasps )
- SOLTY!
- ( screams )
- SHE'S SUICIDAL.
- AXELA, HURRY.
TURN OFF THE POWER.
- I'M WORKING AS FAST AS I CAN.
- JUST A LITTLE CLOSER.
( gasps )
- SOLTY!
- ( crowd cheering )
- Ringmaster: WATERTASTIC.
- I TRIED MY BEST.
- WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU
THINKING UP THERE?
YOU WERE ALMOST KILLED
FOR A ROCK.
- I'M SO SORRY.
I TRIED FOR MORE,
BUT THIS IS ALL I COULD GET.
YOU COULD'VE SAVED SO MANY
PEOPLE IF IT WASN'T FOR ME.
( crying )
CAN YOU EVER FORGIVE ME?
- SILLY GIRL. I WAS ONLY
HALF-SERIOUS, YOU KNOW.
ACTUALLY, IT'S REALLY NOT
ALL THAT BAD DOWN BELOW.
IN FACT, A LOT OF THE PEOPLE
LIVING THERE ARE PRETTY HAPPY.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YEAH, I PROMISE.
- ( chuckles ) THEN THERE'S
NOTHING TO FORGIVE.
- I REALLY LIKE YOU.
YOU SHOULD SERIOUSLY CONSIDER
BECOMING A THIEF, SOLTY.
- HEY, DON'T LISTEN TO HER.
LET'S GO HOME.
- OKAY.
- OH, WHAT A WASTE. I NEED A
DAY OFF FROM THIS DAY OFF.
I'M BEAT.
- WELL, IF NOTHING ELSE
COMES OUT OF THIS,
I'M APPREHENDING ROSE ANDERSON.
- I'LL BE WAITING FOR
YOUR ANSWER. SEE YOU, GIRL!
- COME BACK HERE!
- ( chuckles )
- YOU'RE MINE, ROSE ANDERSON!
- ( sighs ) LET'S GO. MY EARS
CAN'T TAKE ANY MORE OF THIS.
- REGARDING THE EMERALD
STOLEN FROM THE R.U.C. MUSEUM,
I REGRET TO INFORM YOU
THAT OUR ASSIGNMENT
WAS UNSUCCESSFUL.
SORRY, SIR.
WE FAILED TO RETRIEVE IT.
- YOUR APOLOGY IS
UNNECESSARY, INTEGRA.
THE MISSION WAS OF LITTLE
INTEREST TO ME, ANYWAY.
TO BE HONEST, WE WERE SIMPLY
DOING A FAVOR FOR SECTION 1.
HOWEVER,
YOUR FAILURE HAS BROUGHT
SOMETHING FAR MORE INTRIGUING
TO MY ATTENTION.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Solty: ROY KEEPS SEARCHING,
ALWAYS SEARCHING FOR
SOMETHING HE LOST.
NEXT TIME,"BELOVED DAUGHTER."
I HOPE HE FINDS WHAT
HE'S LOOKING FOR SOON.