- HEY, SOLTY!
- WHAT IS IT, KASHA?
- WELL, I KNOW YOU HEAR
ABOUT THIS EVERYDAY,
BUT DO YOU REALLY
UNDERSTAND WHAT RESEMBLE IS?
- NO, I DON'T.
- THEN YOU'D BETTER LEARN!
I GUESS I HAVE NO OTHER CHOICE.
IT'S YOUR LUCKY DAY
BECAUSE I'M GOING TO
TEACH YOU ALL ABOUT IT.
- OH, I CAN'T WAIT.
- WELL, RESEMBLE IS A TECHNOLOGY
THAT USES MECHANICAL PROSTHETICS
TO REPLACE HUMAN BODY PARTS.
- ME?
- NO, NOT YET.
IT JUST BECAME WIDESPREAD
AFTER THE BLAST FALL.
- REALLY?
- BUT LIKE WITH ANY
NEW TECHNOLOGY,
RESEMBLE CAN BE EXPLOITED,
IN THIS CASE TO GIVE PEOPLE
SUPERHUMAN STRENGTH.
THE CRIMINAL ELEMENT HAS
BEEN DOING IT FOR YEARS.
- THAT'S TERRIBLE!
- BUT CRIMINALS AREN'T
THE ONLY ONES WHO USE RESEMBLE.
THERE ARE ALSO PEOPLE
OUT THERE WHO USE IT
- TO HELP OTHERS IN NEED.
- THAT'S REALLY GOOD!
- A PERFECT EXAMPLE IS
THE RESEMBLE RESCUE SQUAD.
THEY CAN EASILY GO PLACES
THAT LARGE EQUIPMENT CAN'T,
AND STILL PERFORM
THE SAME TASKS.
- THAT'S AMAZING!
- OVERKILL.
- OH, SORRY.
- RESEMBLE CONTINUES TO
FIND NEW AND EXCITING USES.
I'LL CONCLUDE
THIS WEEK'S PRESENTATION.
SEE YOU NEXT TIME!
YOU STEPPED ON MY LINE!
- BYE, EVERYBODY!
- YOU STEPPED ON MY LINE!
- WAS THAT BETTER?
- ( Roy speaking )
- ( rumbling )
- ( Rose quivering )
- ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE OKAY, ROSE?
YOU DON'T LOOK VERY GOOD.
- YEAH, I'M ALL RIGHT.
AT LEAST I THINK.
- OH, IT LOOKS LIKE THE
HOLE WE FELL THROUGH
IS COMPLETELY SEALED UP.
- UH-HUH.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Miranda: ROY!
WHAT IN THE WORLD
HAPPENED HERE?
- WE CAME AS SOON AS WE HEARD.
IS IT TRUE?
ROSE AND SOLTY ARE STUCK?
- YEAH. IT HAPPENED JUST AS
WE WERE ABOUT TO CATCH A BOUNTY.
- SO WHY ARE WE STANDING AROUND?
WE'VE GOTTA HELP!
- Rescue leader: IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S NO NEED TO WORRY.
I'M CAPTAIN BARRY VANDELL AND
WE'RE THE RESEMBLE RESCUE SQUAD.
IF YOUR FRIENDS ARE DOWN THERE,
WE'LL FIND 'EM.
JUST LEAVE IT TO US. WE DO
THIS SORT OF THING ALL THE TIME.
WE'LL HAVE THEM OUT
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
- YOU PROMISE?
- YES, I PROMISE.
- Roy: KASHA, YOU HEARD THE MAN.
WE SHOULD JUST SIT BACK AND
LET THESE GUYS DO THEIR JOB.
- AREN'T YOU EVEN WORRIED?
- IT'LL TAKE A LOT MORE THAN
A HOLE IN THE GROUND
TO STOP THOSE GIRLS.
- Rose: ( exclaims )
THIS WAS JUST WHAT I NEEDED!
( giggles )
- UM, CAN I ASK SOMETHING?
- SURE, WHAT'S UP?
- WHY ARE WE TAKING A SHOWER?
- BECAUSE WE WERE
COVERED IN DIRT AND GRIME.
CLEANLINESS SHOULD ALWAYS
BE A TOP PRIORITY.
IT'S JUST ONE OF THOSE THINGS
A GIRL HAS TO DO.
- OH.
- COME ON. SCRUB UP
BEFORE WE RUN OUT OF HOT WATER.
- UM, ROSE?
I REALLY DON'T THINK
THAT'S VERY FLATTERING.
- WHO CARES? IT'S NOT LIKE
ANYBODY CAN SEE ME.
- OKAY THEN, I WON'T LOOK.
- OH, FORGET IT.
IT'S HOPELESS ANYWAY.
I CAN'T PRY THAT THING
OPEN ALL BY MYSELF.
- I WAS WONDERING,
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT THIS PLACE IS?
- OF COURSE I DO.
IT'S THE OLD CITY.
- THE OLD CITY?
- YEAH.
I'M NOT SURE
WHEN THIS ONE WAS BUILT,
BUT IT WAS OBVIOUSLY
A LONG TIME AGO.
I DO KNOW THAT THERE ARE SEVERAL
CITIES, JUST LIKE THIS ONE,
HIDDEN UNDERGROUND.
IT'S PLACES LIKE THIS WHERE
A LOT OF UNREGISTERED CITIZENS
MAKE THEIR HOMES,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE NO ONE'S
LIVED DOWN HERE FOR A LONG TIME.
YOU CAN TELL BECAUSE
EVERYTHING'S SO DILAPIDATED.
( chuckles ) I'M SURPRISED
THAT SHOWER EVEN WORKED.
- OH.
- BUT ALL THAT'S
NOT IMPORTANT NOW.
DO YOU THINK MAYBE
YOU CAN OPEN THIS UP FOR ME?
- I THINK. BUT THEN
WOULDN'T I BE BREAKING A LAW?
- THIS ENTIRE PLACE
IS ABANDONED,
SO IT DOESN'T MATTER.
NOW GET TO WORK.
YOU DON'T WANNA SEE HOW CRABBY
I GET WHEN I'M HUNGRY.
- THEN WE SHOULD HURRY UP
AND FIND A WAY TO
GET OUT OF THIS PLACE.
ROY'S PROBABLY WORRIED ABOUT US.
- OH, YOU THINK SO?
I DOUBT THAT.
- HE ONLY WORRIES ABOUT HIMSELF.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- I WOULDN'T BE SO SURE.
- I KNOW HE IS.
- I KNOW HE'S WORRIED, ROSE!
- OKAY, OKAY.
I'LL TAKE YOUR WORD FOR IT.
NOW WOULD YOU MIND
OPENING THAT FOR ME?
WE'RE GONNA FIND A WAY
OUT OF HERE, RIGHT?
BUT THAT COULD TAKE HOURS,
DAYS, OR EVEN WEEKS.
THAT'S WHY WE SHOULD BE
PREPARED AND HAVE SOME FOOD,
JUST IN CASE WE NEED IT.
- DON'T YOU TRUST ME?
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL DO IT.
- AWESOME! WAY TO GO!
- MOM, CAN'T THESE PEOPLE
WORK ANY FASTER?
AT THIS RATE,
IT'S GONNA BE DARK SOON.
- I KNOW, HONEY,
BUT YOU HAVE TO BE PATIENT.
THIS TYPE OF WORK TAKES TIME.
- I THINK I'VE HAD ALL THE BAD
COFFEE I CAN STAND FOR ONE DAY.
- COME ON, THERE'S
GOT TO BE SOMETHING
WORTH SCAVENGING AROUND HERE.
- ( metallic grazing )
- ROSE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I'M HUNTING FOR TREASURE.
- LET'S GO, ROSE.
THE LONGER WE STAY DOWN HERE,
THE MORE WORRIED
ROY'S GONNA GET.
- HE'S GONNA BE UPSET.
- YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW.
BUT NO ONE HAS
LOOTED THIS AREA YET
AND I'M FINDING
ALL SORTS OF GOOD STUFF.
HERE, HOLD THIS.
THIS IS JUST SOMETHING
TO PASS THE TIME UNTIL
WE FIND OUR
WAY OUT, OKAY?
URGH! ROSE...
- AND BESIDES, LOOK.
SOMETIMES YOU FIND
USEFUL STUFF LIKE THIS.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
THAT IS? A MAP?
- I THINK
IT'S SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
WHAT LANGUAGE
IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
A WORD OF IT.
JUST BY LOOKING AT
THE PICTURES, THOUGH,
IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S A MAP OF
THE UNDERGROUND CITY WE'RE IN.
- ELECTRICAL ROOM,
THE LAUNDRY ROOM.
ENVIRONMENTAL CONTROLS,
INFIRMARY, CAFETERIA.
- WAIT, YOU CAN READ THAT?
- UM, I... YEAH.
- BUT HOW?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- WELL, WHATEVER.
GOOD WORK THOUGH, SOLTY.
NOW, SHOW ME WHERE IT SAYS
THE TREASURE IS LOCATED.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
- OH, I'M JUST KIDDING.
YOU KNOW,
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU SHOULD BE SO CONCERNED
ABOUT WHAT THAT OLD MAN THINKS.
JUST BECAUSE
HE'S YOUR FOSTER PARENT,
- DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVE TO--
- UH, WHAT DOES FOSTER MEAN?
- IT JUST MEANS HE'S NOT
YOUR BIOLOGICAL FATHER.
- BUT ROY IS MY FATHER.
- YEAH, SURE. BUT HE'S...
OH, NEVER MIND. FORGET IT.
WHOA. THAT'S AMAZING.
SO TELL ME,
WHAT IS IT ABOUT ROY
THAT MAKES YOU THINK
SO HIGHLY OF THE GUY?
- THERE'S A BUNCH OF THINGS.
HE'S DONE SO MUCH TO HELP ME.
HE AGREED TO BE MY GUARDIAN
AND HE LETS ME STAY
AT HIS APARTMENT.
HE'S A LOT NICER THAN YOU THINK.
I MEAN, HE HELPED YOU OUT
WHEN YOU NEEDED IT, TOO, RIGHT?
- WELL, YEAH,
I GUESS HE DID. HUH.
- AND YOU TRUST HIM? HONESTLY?
- OF COURSE I TRUST HIM.
- OKAY.
( groans ) OH, MAN,
I'M SO SICK OF THIS.
WHEN ARE WE GONNA
GET OUT OF HERE?
- IT'S OKAY, ROSE. CALM DOWN.
- HAVEN'T YOU REACHED
THE BOTTOM YET?
- WHAT'S TAKING
YOU GUYS SO LONG?
- UH, KASHA.
YELLING AT THEM
ISN'T GOING TO HELP.
THEY'RE DOING THE BEST
THAT THEY CAN. OKAY?
- BUT...
- Rescue leader: GUYS,
I FOUND ONE.
LET'S GO. LET'S GET HIM UP HERE.
DO YOU KNOW THIS ONE?
- Roy: YEAH. THAT'S THE BOUNTY
WE WERE AFTER.
- Worker: CAPTAIN!
- ( humming )
WHAT?
- ARE YOU HUMMING A SONG?
- OH, THAT? IT'S JUST A HABIT.
IT HELPS ME RELAX
AND CONCENTRATE
WHEN MY MIND IS WANDERING.
YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
- OKAY.
( humming )
- ( chuckles )
THAT'S PRETTY BAD, SOLTY.
- OH.
- LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE OUT OF SUPPLIES.
THAT WAS THE LAST
OF THE FOOD AND DRINK.
( sighs ) I'M EXHAUSTED.
HOW MUCH FURTHER
DO YOU THINK WE HAVE TO GO
TILL WE GET OUT OF HERE?
- DON'T WORRY.
I'M SURE WE'RE CLOSE.
- I HOPE SO.
'CAUSE I'M FREAKING TIRED.
- WE CAN'T GIVE UP.
NO MATTER WHAT.
- SO I'VE BEEN THINKING,
IF THAT OLD MAN OF YOURS IS SO
CONCERNED ABOUT OUR WELL-BEING,
THEN SHOULDN'T HE BE
TRYING TO RESCUE US? I MEAN...
- I'M SURE HE'S DOING EVERYTHING
IN HIS POWER TO GET US OUT.
- YOU THINK SO?
- I DO.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- I KNOW SO, REALLY.
- WELL, THEN I HOPE
YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT, ALL THE SAME,
I'M NOT JUST GONNA SIT HERE
AND PLAY THE DAMSEL IN DISTRESS.
AS FUN AS THAT SOUNDS, I
DO HAVE MY PRIDE TO CONSIDER.
SO, LET'S KEEP MOVING, SOLTY.
- OKAY.
- HOW MUCH LONGER IS IT
GONNA TAKE YOU PEOPLE?
YOU BETTER NOT HAVE
BEEN LYING TO ME
WHEN YOU PROMISED TO SAVE THEM!
- YOUNG LADY, YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO BE MORE PATIENT.
MY MEN ARE WORKING
AS FAST AS THEY CAN.
- BUT...
- KASHA, CALM DOWN.
- I'M TIRED OF SITTING. IS THERE
ANYTHING I CAN HELP YOU WITH?
- ( exclaims )
- WHAT'S HE...
- HE'S JUST TRYING TO
KEEP HIMSELF BUSY,
SO HE DOESN'T WORRY.
THAT'S HOW HE IS.
- ( alarm beeping )
- QUICKLY! EVERYBODY
GET OUT! NOW!
IS EVERYONE ALL RIGHT?
ARE THERE ANY INJURIES?
- GREG AND TOM WERE
HURT PRETTY BADLY.
- TAKE 'EM TO THE EV
AND CALL MEDICAL.
- ( crying )
- OH, KASHA. IT'S OKAY.
- Roy: WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU'RE CALLING IT OFF?
THERE ARE TWO LIVES
AT STAKE DOWN THERE!
- THE GROUND'S
BECOME UNSTABLE HERE.
THIS OPERATION WAS ALREADY
DIFFICULT BEFORE THIS HAPPENED.
TO CONTINUE NOW
WOULD BE IMPOSSIBLE.
THERE'S JUST TOO MUCH DEBRIS
FOR MY TEAM TO GET THROUGH.
- Miranda: ROY.
- IF WE KEEP GOING, WE'RE GONNA
RUN INTO SECONDARY CASUALTIES.
IF WE KNEW ANOTHER WAY
TO GET DOWN THERE,
IT WOULD BE A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT STORY.
LOOK, I'M SORRY, I REALLY AM.
BUT I NEED TO CONSIDER
THE SAFETY OF MY MEN, TOO.
- I'LL DO IT MYSELF
IF I HAVE TO.
- ROY, DON'T!
- Andy: SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF
WORK FOR SUCH AN OLD MAN.
- EXCUSE ME, WHO ARE YOU?
- I CALLED FOR THEM.
THEIR SISTER ROSE IS ONE OF
THE PEOPLE TRAPPED UNDERGROUND.
- HEY, BUDDY, FIRST OFF
I LOVE THE OUTFIT.
NOW DIDN'T I HEAR YOU SAY THAT
IF YOU KNEW ANOTHER WAY INSIDE,
YOU COULD PROBABLY RESCUE THEM?
- YES. WHY?
- WE HAPPEN TO KNOW ONE.
- THE PLACE IS SO OLD,
WE HAD A HELLUVA TIME
GETTING OUR HANDS ON THIS.
- IT'S THE COMPLETE
STRUCTURAL LAYOUT
FOR THE UNDERGROUND
CITY BELOW US.
- Rescue leader: AND YOU'RE
SURE THIS IS THE RIGHT SPOT?
- Larry: POSITIVE.
THERE'S AN AIR CIRCULATION VENT
DIRECTLY BELOW US
THAT WAS PAVED OVER
WHEN THE CITY WAS ABANDONED.
ITS DIAMETER
IS AROUND FOUR METERS.
- WILL THAT BE ENOUGH?
- YES. MORE THAN ENOUGH.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, LET'S BREAK
THROUGH THIS CONCRETE. MOVE!
- YES, CAPTAIN. WE'RE ON IT,
CAPTAIN! YES, SIR.
- SO, YOU STILL UP
FOR HELPING US OUT?
- DAMN RIGHT I AM.
- I'M LISTENING. WHAT'S THIS?
- Andy: THIS IS THE
EXTERNAL CONDUIT
FOR THE COMPUTER SYSTEM
THAT RUNS THE CITY.
I CAN CONTROL THE ENTIRE GRID
FROM UP HERE IF I NEED TO.
SEE, THESE OLD CITIES
WERE BUILT USING COMPUTERS
THAT ARE ARCHAIC TODAY.
THEY ALL USE
PROPRIETARY GEAR
THAT YOU CAN'T
REALLY FIND ANYMORE.
LUCKILY FOR ME, I HAVE
A FRIEND WHO'S A PACK RAT.
- CAN YOU MAKE IT WORK?
- I CAN DO THIS STUFF
IN MY SLEEP.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I DON'T KNOW.
THE SYSTEM'S UNSTABLE
AND IT'S BEGINNING TO OVERHEAT.
SO DARN OLD,
THE WIRING'S PROBABLY SHOT.
- CAN YOU WORK AROUND IT?
- I THINK SO.
OKAY I'M INSIDE. HOLD ON.
I'M DOWNLOADING THE SCHEMATICS
TO MY LAPTOP.
- ( beeping )
- HEY, UH,
WHAT'S ALL THAT RED STUFF?
- OH, MY GOD, THIS IS BAD.
LOOKS LIKE
THE WHOLE CITY'S ON FIRE.
- WHAT CAN DO YOU?
CAN YOU, LIKE, TAP INTO A CAMERA
AND FIND OUT
WHERE THEY ARE OR SOMETHING?
- JUST HOLD ON.
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN PULL UP.
DAMMIT! NO GOOD.
CAMERA SYSTEM'S TOTALLY DOWN.
- Rescue leader: GUYS,
CARE TO EXPLAIN THIS?
- Larry: EXCELLENT WORK. YOU'RE
RIGHT WHERE YOU NEED TO BE.
NOW JUST REMOVE
THAT STEEL PLATE
AND YOU'LL FIND THE
VENT UNDERNEATH.
ONCE THAT'S DONE,
YOU CAN GET INSIDE.
- OKAY, TEAM, LET'S GET READY
TO PRY IT OPEN.
- WHAT'S THIS?
I'M HAVING TROUBLE EVEN GETTING
THE SPRINKLER SYSTEM TO ENGAGE.
OH, NO. YOU'VE GOT
TO BE KIDDING ME!
ACCORDING TO THIS, THE FIRE
HAS SPREAD TO THE FUEL DEPOT.
- I THINK IT STOPPED.
- THAT WAS
AN ENORMOUS EXPLOSION.
NO TELLING
HOW MUCH DAMAGE IT DID.
I SURE HOPE IT DOESN'T
INTERRUPT MY CONNECTION.
- MOM...
- LIFT!
- GREAT. THAT DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE A VENT TO ME.
- Larry: IT'S A
PROTECTIVE SHUTTER.
- YOU THINK YOU CAN OPEN IT?
- GUESS WE'LL FIND OUT.
- ( beeping )
- WHAT!
THIS IS STARTING TO PISS ME OFF.
IF IT'S NOT ONE THING,
IT'S ANOTHER!
- WHAT IS IT?
- THE DAMN FIRE'S BURNED OFF
ALMOST ALL THE OXYGEN.
THEY'RE GONNA SUFFOCATE
DOWN THERE!
- THEN HURRY UP AND OPEN IT!
- I KNOW!
JUST GIVE ME A SECOND!
OH, NO. THE ENTIRE SYSTEM
JUST SHUT ITSELF DOWN.
- IS THERE ANY OTHER WAY
WE CAN OPEN THAT SHUTTER?
- YOU MEAN...
- COME ON!
- HEY, TAKE A BREAK, PAL.
WE'RE GONNA FIND A WAY
TO OPEN THIS THING UP, OKAY.
JAMES, GET THE ELECTRIC SAW
OVER HERE!
- CAPTAIN, WE'LL HAVE MORE LUCK
DOING IT BY HAND.
- I DON'T CARE HOW YOU DO IT.
JUST GET IT OPEN!
- Roy: DAMMIT.
DAMMIT!
( quivering ) I CAN'T...
I CAN'T LOSE ANOTHER ONE.
NOT AGAIN.
- ROY.
- ( rumbling )
- YOU HEAR THAT?
- WHAT THE HELL IS...
BACK UP!
- ( Solty yelling )
- SOLTY!
THANK GOODNESS!
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE ALL RIGHT!
- ROSE. ROSE!
- OH, UH, HEY GUYS.
- I DON'T KNOW WHO YOU ARE,
BUT IF YOU'RE EVER LOOKING
FOR A JOB, GIVE US A CALL.
- OH, UH...
- ( exhales )
LET'S GO HOME.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Solty: THERE'S
SOMETHING BIG
THAT I'M REALLY
LOOKING FORWARD TO!
- Rose: OH, YEAH.
IT'S THE OLD MAN'S
BIRTHDAY, RIGHT?
- ( exclaims )
NEXT EPISODE, "BIRTHDAY GAME."
SHH, IT'S A SECRET.