- Yuto: TWELVE YEARS AGO,
OUR CITY WAS STRUCK BY DISASTER.
THE INCIDENT CAME TO BE
KNOWN AS THE BLAST FALL.
MANY PEOPLE DIED THAT DAY.
AND STILL MORE WERE NEVER FOUND.
FOR THE SURVIVORS, MANY OF
THEIR INJURIES WERE SO SEVERE
THAT REGAINING A NORMAL QUALITY
OF LIFE SEEMED IMPOSSIBLE.
BUT WHERE FLESH
AND BONE PROVED TO FAIL,
TECHNOLOGY PROVIDED THE
ANSWER THROUGH ENHANCEMENTS.
CYBERNETICS.
( Yuto speaking )
- ( beeping )
- THIS MEANS THAT SHE'S...
- SHE'S A CYBORG.
- OUTWARDLY SHE MAY LOOK
AS HUMAN AS ANYONE,
BUT IT'S THE BEST HUMAN
MONEY CAN BUY.
THERE'S NOT A SINGLE
ORGANIC PART ON HER.
SHE'S A PERFECT SPECIMEN
OF RESEMBLE TECHNOLOGY.
- WAIT A SECOND, I DON'T GET IT.
- SEE, RESEMBLE IS
MECHANICAL REPLACEMENTS
FOR HUMAN BODY PARTS.
YOU CAN REPLACE A PINKY,
OR AN ENTIRE ARM.
BUT, ACCORDING TO THE DATA,
THIS PARTICULAR BODY
ISN'T JUST YOUR ORDINARY,
RUN-OF-THE-MILL RES.
IT'S MAN-MADE. CREATED BY
HUMAN HANDS FROM HEAD TO TOE.
- DOES THAT INCLUDE HER BRAIN?
- ABSOLUTELY.
HERE'S A PUBLISHED ARTICLE
ON RESEMBLE TECHNOLOGY
THAT SAYS THE MAXIMUM
LEVEL OF REPLACEMENT
IS CURRENTLY AT 60 PERCENT.
BUT, AS MY CALCULATIONS CONFIRM,
THIS BODY IS 100
PERCENT RESEMBLE.
DON'T YOU GET HOW COMPLETELY
MIND-BLOWING THIS IS?
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
AN UNPRECEDENTED MARRIAGE
BETWEEN STATE-OF-THE
ART TECHNOLOGY
AND SYNTHETIC HUMANOID SYSTEMS.
A TRUE BODY OF ART. AND THE
OWNER OF THAT BODY
IS STANDING RIGHT HERE
BEFORE OUR EYES.
SOLTY!
- IS EATING A...
- OH, IT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
TODAY'S RESEMBLE TECHNOLOGY
CAN DUPLICATE THE BODY'S ENTIRE
DIGESTIVE SYSTEM PERFECTLY.
- I FIND IT A LITTLE HARD
TO BELIEVE SOLTY IS A MACHINE.
- NO WONDER I THOUGHT
SHE WAS A LITTLE STRANGE.
- ( sighs )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING
DIFFERENT ABOUT SOLTY.
BUT TO LEARN SHE'S A ROBOT
IS JUST A SHOCK.
- CALLING HER A ROBOT IS AN
INSULT. SOLTY IS A MASTERPIECE
OF RESEMBLE
PROSTHETICS TECHNOLOGY.
- A MASTERPIECE?
YEAH, RIGHT!
- WELL, I SUPPOSE IT ALL
DOES MAKES SENSE NOW.
RIGHT, ROY?
- YEAH. SORT OF.
- COME ON.
YOU MUST BE AT LEAST
SLIGHTLY RELIEVED
TO KNOW THAT SOLTY ISN'T HUMAN.
- OH, SHUT UP.
- ( laughs )
- DOES ANYONE KNOW
WHERE SOLTY WENT?
- PROBABLY OUT ON
HER USUAL WALK.
- ( crying )
- UH, HEY. WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- UH...
- I UNDERSTAND.
YOU'RE LOST, AREN'T YOU?
- MMM-HMM.
MY MOMMY HURT HER LEG.
SHE TOLD ME TO GO
GROCERY SHOPPING FOR HER,
BUT I GOT LOST AND NOW
I DON'T KNOW WHERE I AM.
IF I COULD GET TO THE STATION,
I KNOW I COULD FIND MY WAY HOME.
- YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A STATION?
- WILL YOU PLEASE TAKE ME THERE?
- I'M SORRY, I DON'T KNOW
WHERE IT IS EITHER.
NO, NO, PLEASE.
PLEASE DON'T CRY.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL HELP YOU.
WE ARE GONNA FIND
THIS STATION TOGETHER.
- REALLY?
- THANK YOU.
- HI. MY NAME'S SOLTY
REVANT. WHO ARE YOU?
- MERYL TYLER. NICE TO MEET YOU.
- ( train horn whistling )
- ( exclaiming excitedly )
- SOLTY!
- WHAT IS IT?
- YOU GOT ON THE TRAIN WITH ME.
- GUESS I DID. I DIDN'T REALLY
KNOW WHAT TO DO,
BUT I GUESS NOW I CAN HELP YOU
ALL THE WAY TO YOUR HOUSE.
- THE RIDE DOES
TAKE ABOUT AN HOUR.
- ( giggles )
EARLIER YOU SAID
YOUR MOMMY WAS HURT.
IT'S NOTHING SERIOUS, I HOPE.
- SHE'LL BE OKAY. SHE JUST
NEEDS TO REST A LITTLE WHILE.
MY DADDY AND I HAVE BEEN DOING
ALL THE SHOPPING FOR HER.
- YOU'RE LUCKY TO HAVE
A DADDY WHO CARES.
- WHAT ABOUT YOUR DADDY?
IS HE NOT VERY NICE?
- UH, YES. HE'S KINDA NICE.
BUT HE'S ALSO SCARY.
WHEN HE'S REALLY ANGRY.
HE GETS WRINKLES RIGHT HERE.
- MY DAD CAN GET ANGRY TOO.
MAYBE IT'S HIS WORK.
- I GUESS SO.
- HEY, I KNOW A SECRET.
IT WORKS GREAT AND CHEERS
MY DADDY UP EVERY TIME HE'S SAD.
MY MOMMY TAUGHT IT TO ME.
- THAT SOUNDS AMAZING. DO YOU
THINK YOU COULD TEACH IT TO ME?
- OKAY. IT'S...
( whispering )
- OH...
- REALLY. IT WORKS!
- THANKS. I'LL GIVE IT A TRY.
- JUST AS OUR INTEL PREDICTED.
- ( gasps )
- JACKSON MCLEAN.
DEATH ROW INMATE NUMBER 1467.
AND TEST SUBJECT NUMBER 43-85,
AM I CORRECT?
- AND YOU MUST BE R.U.C.
- YOUR BODY IS 78
PERCENT RESEMBLE.
DURING A SYSTEMS TEST,
YOU ESCAPED BY
ILLEGALLY DESTROYING
BOTH THE SAFETY MECHANISM
AND TRACKING BEACON.
IT TOOK QUITE A FEW
MAN-HOURS TO FIND YOU.
- SO, HOW'D YOU KNOW
I'D BE HERE?
- YOU UNDERESTIMATE
OUR RESOURCES, MCLEAN.
- WHAT? WHO TOLD YOU? I...
- AND FRANKLY, YOUR MOVEMENTS
ARE QUITE PREDICTABLE.
- ( beeping )
- GOT THEM. EXCELLENT
WORK, AXELA. - THANKS.
- I ADVISE YOU TO
RETURN QUIETLY!
- ( scoffs ) AND IF I REFUSE?
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps )
- CHOOSE. WHAT'LL IT BE, MCLEAN?
- ( laughing )
- ( exclaims )
- DAMMIT!
- THAT WAS PAINFUL. I CAN'T AIM
WITH ALL THE SPOTS IN MY EYES.
I WANNA GO HOME!
- Silvia: CELICA,
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
- CAN YOU STILL TRACK HIM?
- IT'LL TAKE TIME.
- Silvia: WHAT'S YOUR CALL,
INTEGRA?
- Celica: LET'S PACK IT UP
AND TRY AGAIN TOMORROW.
- Silvia: NOBODY ASKED YOU,
CELICA. INTEGRA?
- Integra: LET'S WITHDRAW,
FOR NOW.
- UGH! AFFIRMATIVE.
- Celica: THANK YOU!
- Integra:
WE UNDERESTIMATED HIM.
TIME TO RETHINK OUR STRATEGY.
- ( TV playing indistinctly )
- MOMMY, I'M BACK!
- WELCOME HOME, HONEY.
THANK YOU FOR
HELPING MY DAUGHTER.
IT'S SUCH A MIRACLE THAT YOU
CAME ALONG WHEN YOU DID.
- IT WAS NOTHING.
- WHY DON'T YOU JOIN
US FOR DINNER?
- ME?
- YEAH, SOLTY.
EAT DINNER WITH US.
- UM, I'M NOT...
- WANT TO HELP YOUR
MOMMY IN THE KITCHEN?
- UH-HUH!
- JUST MAKE YOURSELF COMFY.
I'LL PUT ON SOME TEA.
- UH...
- Man on TV: THIS PROGRAM IS
BROUGHT TO YOU BY R.U.C.
R.U.C. TECHNOLOGY THAT
MAKES LIFE WORTH LIVING.
- NOW REMEMBER, MERYL, WHEN
SOMEONE SHOWS YOU KINDNESS,
YOU SHOULD ALWAYS
REPAY IT IN KIND.
- I KNOW.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, SOLTY?
DID WE SAY SOMETHING WRONG?
- UH, NO, MERYL. IT ISN'T THAT.
IT'S JUST...
YOUR HOUSE IS VERY BEAUTIFUL.
I CAN'T HELP BUT FEEL
HAPPY JUST BEING HERE.
- WELL, IT MAKES ME FEEL
VERY HAPPY TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
- ( door opens )
- I'M HOME!
AND I SEE WE HAVE A VISITOR.
- ( laughing ) DADDY!
- HELLO MY LITTLE PRINCESS.
HOW'S YOUR LEG, HONEY?
- ACTUALLY, IT'S FEELING
MUCH BETTER TODAY.
- GOOD, I'M GLAD TO HEAR THAT.
AND WHO IS THIS YOUNG LADY?
- I'M SORRY, SIR.
MY NAME IS SOLTY REVANT.
- SHE WAS KIND ENOUGH
TO HELP MERYL MAKE IT HOME.
- WE ASKED HER TO EAT
DINNER WITH US.
- WELL, THAT WAS NICE.
AREN'T WE HONORED TO HAVE
SUCH A CONSIDERATE GUEST.
( chuckles ) LUCKY FOR YOU,
I'M NOT COOKING TONIGHT.
- ( all laugh )
- FAMILY.
( gasps )
( screams )
- Meryl: SOLTY, WHAT'S WRONG?
- I DIDN'T REALIZE
IT WAS SO LATE!
PLEASE FORGIVE ME. I GOT TO GO.
- WAIT, SOLTY?
- YES?
- UM, MAYBE...
MAYBE TOMORROW?
- ( exclaims happily ) SURE.
SEE YOU THEN.
- ( door opens )
- Solty: IT WAS NICE
MEETING YOU.
- WELL, THAT'S A SHAME.
- YEAH. ANOTHER TIME PERHAPS.
- MMM-HMM.
- Yuto: I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
LOOK AT WHAT TIME IT IS.
SHE'S BEEN GONE WAY TOO LONG.
- I THINK YUTO'S RIGHT.
SHOULDN'T WE CALL THE POLICE?
TO BE SAFE?
- WHAT'S THE POINT?
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY'D
ACTUALLY DO ANYTHING.
- HMM.
- WHAT THE HECK ARE
YOU WAITING FOR?
AREN'T YOU THE LEAST BIT
WORRIED ABOUT SOLTY?
YOU DO REALIZE THERE
ARE PLENTY OF PEOPLE
WHO'D LOVE TO GET HOLD
OF HER TECHNOLOGY.
- ( slurping )
- ( sighs )
WHAT'S WITH HIM?
HOW CAN HE BE SO COLD?
ISN'T HE SUPPOSED
TO BE A PARENT?
- HE IS A PARENT.
HE'S JUST NOT VERY
GOOD AT SHOWING
OTHER PEOPLE HIS FEELINGS.
- COME ON!
SHE'S A ROBOT! WHAT THE
HELL AM I WORRIED FOR?
( sighs )
DAMMIT!
- ( door opens )
- HELLO. I'M BACK.
TODAY WAS AMAZING.
I MET THIS NICE,
LITTLE GIRL WHO WAS LOST.
HER NAME IS MERYL TYLER
AND WE BECAME FRIENDS.
AND MERYL NEEDED TO FIND THE
TRAIN STATION, SO I HELPED HER.
WE ENDED UP AT HER HOUSE.
IT'S BIG AND BEAUTIFUL.
SHE INVITED ME BACK TOMORROW,
AND I SAID YES.
- ( snoring )
- UH-OH. HE LOOKS ANGRY.
VERY ANGRY.
- I KNOW A SECRET.
IT WORKS GREAT AND CHEERS
MY DADDY UP EVERY TIME HE'S SAD.
MY MOMMY TAUGHT IT TO ME.
- NOW'S THE TIME TO TRY IT.
I SURE HOPE THIS WORKS.
- UM, I, UH...
- SPIT IT OUT.
- WELL, SEE, I...
- JUST SAY IT!
- I, UH...
- I'M TRYING TO SLEEP HERE.
- DADDY, I LOVE YOU.
- UH...
I LOVE YOU.
- ( footsteps )
- ( door closes )
- ( Roy panting )
- ROY, WHAT'S WRONG?
- SOLTY...
- SOLTY CAME HOME?
- SHE'S GONE...
SHE'S CRAZY.
- I COULD HAVE TOLD YOU THAT.
NO ONE LISTENS.
- OH, MERYL, YOUR SECRET
DIDN'T WORK ON ROY.
- OH, SHE'S GONE AGAIN?
- YES. DO YOU HAVE ANY
IDEA WHERE SHE IS?
- SOLTY LEFT.
SHE SAID SHE PROMISED A FRIEND
THAT SHE'D GO BACK AND SEE HER.
- WHY DIDN'T SHE TELL ME?
- AND MERYL NEEDED TO
FIND THE TRAIN STATION,
SO I HELPED HER.
WE ENDED UP AT HER HOUSE.
IT'S BIG AND BEAUTIFUL.
SHE INVITED ME BACK TOMORROW.
- YOU OKAY, ROY?
- IT'S... IT'S NOTHING.
- ( chuckles )
SEE, YUTO.
HE KNOWS HOW TO BE A PARENT.
- THEN HE'S SURE GOOD
AT HIDING IT.
- Meryl: REALLY?
SO IT DIDN'T WORK AT ALL?
- NO, I GUESS NOT.
SO, ENOUGH ABOUT ALL THAT.
WHAT ARE WE SHOPPING FOR TODAY?
- LET ME CHECK AND SEE.
- ( beeps )
- ( giggles )
WOW. THAT'S A LOT OF FOOD.
- I KNOW.
MAYBE WE BOUGHT TOO MUCH.
- YOU MUST BE TIRED.
WAIT HERE AND I'LL GET
US SOMETHING TO DRINK.
- DO YOU NEED MONEY?
- DON'T WORRY.
I'VE GOT IT COVERED.
SEE. I HAVE ONE, TOO!
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
I WON'T BE LONG.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
- Celica: TARGET SIGHTED.
GOTCHA. HE'S MINE.
I'VE GOT THE PERFECT SHOT.
JUST SAY THE WORD.
- Integra: NEGATIVE!
DO NOT FIRE.
OUR FIRST PRIORITY
IS TO KEEP A LOW PROFILE.
- HE ESCAPED ONCE.
I CAN TAKE HIM DOWN.
- NO, WE CAN'T RISK
CIVILIAN CASUALTIES.
- EXCUSE ME, MISTER,
BUT YOU DON'T LOOK SO GOOD.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
ARE YOU SICK?
- MERYL? THAT'S STRANGE.
WHERE WOULD SHE HAVE GONE?
- ( screams )
- ( gasps ) DOWN THERE!
- ( clanking )
- ( Meryl crying )
- THOSE BADGES KNOW
EVERY MOVE I MAKE.
- BUT THANKS TO YOU, SWEETNESS,
EVEN THEY WOULDN'T TOUCH ME NOW.
- SOLTY!
- MERYL!
- ( grunting )
- HOW'D YOU STOP THAT?
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- WHAT WERE YOU DOING
WITH MY FRIEND?
- TELL ME YOUR NAME,
LITTLE GIRL.
- I'M SOLTY. WHO ARE YOU?
- ( groaning ) WHAT THE?
- ( screams )
- YOU'RE IN MY WAY!
- DON'T HURT HER!
- ( groaning )
- ( laughing )
- Meryl: SOLTY, WAKE UP. SOLTY!
- Roy: NO, YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND, OFFICER.
I NEED TO SEE THAT ID CARD.
YOU FOUND IT HERE?
- CALM DOWN, SIR.
NOW, WHO IS SHE?
- SOLTY REVANT!
- WELL, SIR ALL WE
KNOW IS THAT THE CARD
WAS FOUND NEAR ONE
OF THESE PACKAGES.
I GUESS SHE DROPPED IT.
- WHAT ELSE? DO YOU HAVE ANY
LEADS ON HER LOCATION?
- PATROLS ARE COMBING THE AREA.
NOW, YOU CAN HELP US BY
ANSWERING SOME QUESTIONS.
WHAT'S YOUR RELATIONSHIP
TO THIS MISSING PERSON?
- ( scoffs ) THIS ISN'T GOOD.
PEOPLE ARE STARTING TO GATHER.
- LOCAL LAW
ENFORCEMENT CONFIRMS
THE TWO GIRLS' FAMILIES
HAVE BEEN NOTIFIED.
- WE NEED ORDERS?
THE LONGER WE WAIT, THE
BIGGER THE CROWD'S GONNA GET.
- Integra: AND IF WE MOVE IN
TOO SOON, WE RISK FAILURE.
- YEAH WELL, UNLESS THE
TARGET DECIDES TO SURFACE,
I'VE GOT NOTHING TO DO.
- PREP THE SUIT. I'M GOING IN.
- Silvia: YOU GOING
TO ELIMINATE HIM?
- WE CANNOT COMPROMISE
THE INTELLIGENCE.
- Silvia: WHAT ABOUT
THE TWO CAPTIVES?
- YOU ALREADY KNOW
THE ANSWER TO THAT.
- Silvia: UNDERSTOOD.
- AXELA, LET'S MOVE IT,
POWER UP THE SYSTEM.
FORGO THE SAFETY CHECK.
- RIGHT.
ALL SYSTEMS INITIALIZED.
ATTACH GEL RINGS.
COCOON ENGAGED
AND PREPPED FOR SAFE ENTRY.
PROBE ARRAY CONNECTED.
BIOFEEDBACK ON STANDBY.
- ( rock song playing )
- GEL COAT COMPLETE.
ARMOR COAT STANDING BY.
P.S.D. CONVERSION COMPLETE.
- SILVIA.
- I READ YOU. WHAT'S THE PLAN.
- I'LL STRIKE ON THE
TARGET'S NEXT MOVE.
APPRISE ME ON THE DETAILS.
- ROGER THAT!
- ( Meryl crying )
- ( clanking )
- ( grunting ) DAMMIT!
DAMMIT WE'RE TRAPPED!
SHUT UP! SHUT YOUR
ROTTEN LITTLE MOUTH!
- ( screaming )
- YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE DEAD.
- SOLTY.
- ( gasps ) IMPOSSIBLE!
- I HATE YOU!
- ( Meryl screams )
- ( gasps ) EASY.
( screams )
- YOU'RE BAD.
I HATE BAD PEOPLE!
- ( screams )
- ( siren wailing )
- ( whimpers )
- ( wind blowing )
- ( crying )
- THAT'S IT.
HE CAN'T HURT YOU NOW, MERYL.
- NO!
- DON'T WORRY. I'M HERE.
DON'T COME NEAR ME. LET ME GO.
- Man: YEAH, BUT WHO TOOK HER?
- MOMMY! DADDY!
- OH, SWEETIE!
- WE WERE SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- HOLD ON. I THINK THAT'S...
- Integra:
PREPARE FOR RETRIEVAL!
- UNDERSTOOD.
- WONDER IF I GET
OVERTIME FOR THIS?
- MERYL. SHE'S MY FIRST FRIEND.
BUT, I DON'T THINK SHE
LIKES ME ANYMORE.
I SCARE HER.
- I WANNA GO HOME! PLEASE HURRY!
- IT'S OKAY BABY,
YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
- ( crying )
- Roy: SHE'LL
UNDERSTAND SOMEDAY.
LET'S GO HOME, OKAY?
- OKAY.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Solty: WOW. I'VE NEVER SEEN
SUCH A HUGE BATH BEFORE.
NEXT TIME, "WATERSIDE PANIC."
UM, WAIT, DO I KNOW YOU?