- Miranda: IT WAS 12 YEARS AGO.
THE DAY THAT CHANGED
ALL OF OUR LIVES.
A POWERFUL BOLT OF LIGHTNING
FROM THE AURORA SHELL
STRUCK THE OLD
R.U.C. HEADQUARTERS.
- ( gasping )
- IT WAS THE DISASTER THAT CAME
TO BE KNOWN AS THE BLAST FALL.
( Miranda speaking )
- HELLO! AND WELCOME TO
MAVERICK HUNTERS AGENCY!
WE'RE HERE WHEN YOU NEED US,
ANY TIME DAY OR NIGHT.
WHETHER IT'S SEARCHING
FOR YOUR LOST CAT,
OR TRACKING DOWN A CAT BURGLAR,
WHEN SOMETHING NEEDS FINDING,
COUNT ON OUR TEAM OF
PROFESSIONAL HUNTERS--
- IMPERTINENT BITCH.
LOOK AT HER.
MAKING A MOCKERY
OF OUR PROFESSION.
- SOMEONE SHOULD TEACH HER
SOME RESPECT. GET ME?
- THANKS FOR THE ORDER!
- 8,50,000 TORAS.
THERE YOU GO,
THE MONEY'S BEEN WIRED
TO YOUR ACCOUNT.
THANK YOU,
GREAT WORK, AS ALWAYS!
- YEAH, AND YOU LOOK
REALLY GOOD UP THERE.
- THANK YOU.
-JUST LET ME KNOW IF
YOU GOT ANY MORE JOBS
YOU WANNA SEND MY WAY
- DEFINITELY.
- ALL RIGHT, WELL I'LL...
- ...SO WHATEVER YOUR PROBLEM,
COME TO MAVERICK HUNTERS AGENCY.
YOU'LL BE GLAD YOU DID!
- Woman on TV: THAT WAS
MIRANDA MAVERICK,
OWNER AND OPERATOR OF
MAVERICK HUNTERS AGENCY,
ONE OF SEVERAL
UP-AND-COMING BUSINESSES...
- GUESS THIS IS ABOUT
THAT DALE BOYD,
GRAY WALKER INCIDENT YESTERDAY?
- YEP.
- Kasha: WHAT'S WITH YOU?
YOU ALWAYS GOTTA BE
SO GRUMPY ALL THE TIME?
I MEAN, YOU JUST
WALK INTO THE ROOM,
AND ALL THE OTHER
HUNTERS SCATTER.
- NOW, KASHA...
- LUCKY FOR YOU, YOU GOT TALENT.
'CAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
I CAN SEE MOM PUTS UP WITH YOU.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- YEAH.
( grunts )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( police radio chattering )
- UH-HUH. I SEE.
SO, THIS IS WHERE YOU SAY
SOMEONE TOOK A SHOT AT YOU?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- THANKS, THAT'S ALL I NEED.
- WAIT A SECOND. YOU'RE LEAVING?
AREN'T YOU GONNA DO SOMETHING?
- OH, AND IF YOU WANT US TO
OPEN AN OFFICIAL INVESTIGATION,
YOU'LL NEED TO COME DOWN
TO THE STATION TOMORROW
WITH YOUR CITIZEN ID CARD
AND FILE A REPORT.
IN THE MEANTIME,
HAVE A NICE DAY.
- WHAT, SO YOU MEAN THAT'S IT?
OF ALL THE STUPID,
GOOD-FOR-NOTHING...
- AND WHAT DID YOU EXPECT?
IT'S THE POLICE.
SO WHAT NOW?
- I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
OH, I DON'T SUPPOSE I COULD
HIRE YOU AS MY BODYGUARD AGAIN.
THINK YOU'D BE UP TO IT?
- SURE.
NOT LIKE I HAVE
MUCH OF A CHOICE.
ALL CLEAR.
NO SIGNS OF A BREAK-IN.
- WELL, THAT'S A RELIEF,
AT LEAST.
- NOW, YOU NEED TO...
- WE KNOW.
WE NEED TO KEEP THE
LIGHTS TURNED OFF
AND STAY AWAY FROM THE
WINDOWS. THAT IT?
- YEAH, SOMETHIN' LIKE THAT.
- IT REALLY IS A BIG HELP
HAVING YOU RIGHT HERE
IN THE SAME BUILDING.
- I'LL BE IN MY APARTMENT.
JUST SHOUT IF YOU NEED ME.
- ALL RIGHT, THEN.
GOOD NIGHT.
- OH, WE FORGOT TO COORDINATE
A SCHEDULE WITH ROY
FOR IN THE MORNING, DIDN'T WE?
- OH, YEAH.
- COME ON. NOW'S NOT THE TIME
TO START GETTIN' SLOPPY.
WE'RE GONNA DO THAT,
RIGHT NOW!
- YEAH, I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
- ROY! ROY!
WHAT HAPPENED? WHOA!
- UH, ROY?
OH.
WHO IS SHE, ROY?
SHE'S ADORABLE!
- YEAH, WHO THE HECK IS SHE?
- YOU'RE SO CUTE!
- BEATS ME.
- BUT SHE WAS IN YOUR APARTMENT!
- 'CAUSE SHE BROKE IN.
- WAIT, YOU'VE NEVER
SEEN HER BEFORE.
- SO ARE YOU READY
TO TALK TO US?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME, DEAR?
WHERE'D YOU COME FROM?
- I'M SORRY. I REALLY...
I REALLY JUST DON'T KNOW.
- THERE, YOU HAPPY?
JUST THROW HER OUT.
- OH, ROY, STOP IT.
THAT'S JUST MEAN.
- SO WHAT'S THIS YOU'VE GOT
GOING ON WITH YOUR EARS HERE?
SOME KIND OF NEW RESEMBLE FAD?
NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE IT.
- ( exclaims )
- UH, SORRY.
- WELL, ANYWAY,
MAYBE WE COULD LET HER
STAY WITH US FOR THE NIGHT.
YOU THINK? I MEAN, SHE SEEMS
LIKE A NICE ENOUGH GIRL.
- OKAY WITH YOU?
- ALL RIGHT. SUIT YOURSELF.
- THEN THAT SETTLES IT.
- ( sighs )
- Kasha: MOM, CAN WE TALK?
- SURE, HON, WHAT IS IT?
- HAVE YOU COMPLETELY
LOST YOUR MIND?
SOMEONE IS TRYING TO KILL YOU!
SO WHY WOULD YOU PICK TODAY,
OF ALL DAYS, TO DECIDE
TO GO SHOPPING?
- WELL, UH...
- I MEAN, DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S JUST A LITTLE DANGEROUS
TO BE OUT IN PUBLIC LIKE THIS?
- I KNOW, BUT I FELT SO SORRY
FOR HER LOOKING LIKE THAT.
POOR THING.
MY CLOTHES ARE WAY TOO BIG FOR
HER, AND YOURS ARE TOO SMALL.
- I STILL THINK WE SHOULD
GO HOME. RIGHT, ROY?
- ALL THE SAME TO ME.
- Miranda: LET'S GO, DEAR!
- Woman: LOOK AT HER.
- OH, I SAW YOU ON TV YESTERDAY.
YOU'RE SO MUCH PRETTIER
IN PERSON.
- THANKS, THAT'S
VERY KIND OF YOU.
- HEY, I THOUGHT
WE CAME HERE TO SHOP.
- OH, YES, RIGHT. ( chuckles )
WELL, I GUESS I'LL BE GOING NOW.
IT WAS... IT WAS NICE
CHATTING WITH YOU!
- ( gasps )
- OKAY, WHAT ABOUT THIS ONE?
- EH. MAKES HER LOOK
LIKE A LITTLE KID.
- THEN HOW ABOUT THIS?
- TOO FLASHY.
- OOH! THIS!
- TOO LAME.
- WHICH OF THESE DO YOU THINK
IS CUTER?
ROY?
WHICH DO YOU LIKE BETTER,
THIS ONE? OR THIS ONE?
- DON'T ASK ME.
- THEN BETWEEN THIS ONE
OR THIS ONE?
- I WOULDN'T KNOW.
- THIS, OR THIS?
- DON'T CARE.
- OKAY. THIS ONE...
- IT'S FINE.
SURE, WHATEVER, I LOVE IT.
- Kasha: REALLY?
- Miranda: MM, I DON'T KNOW.
- IT'S KIND OF DORKY, HONESTLY.
- I'M SURE WE COULD FIND
SOMETHING A BIT MORE FLATTERING.
- I LIKE IT.
THIS IS THE ONE I WANT.
- YOU'RE SURE?
- YOU HEARD HER.
THIS IS THE ONE.
- ( giggles )
- SO WHAT'RE YOU TRYIN' TO PULL?
WHY DID YOU BREAK INTO MY PLACE?
I THOUGHT I SPELLED IT OUT
PRETTY CLEAR.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR YOU.
- UM, I, UH...
I REALLY DO LOVE
THESE NEW CLOTHES. I DO!
I NEVER, EVER
WANNA TAKE THEM OFF!
- ( sighs )
- HEY! I GOT US SOME LUNCH!
- OH, COMING!
- SO, ARE YOU HAVING FUN, ROY?
- YEAH.
- ME, TOO.
AND JUST LOOK AT THE GIRLS,
GETTING ALONG SO WELL.
- YOU'VE NEVER EATEN A HAMBURGER
BEFORE? ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WHAT ARE YOU, LIKE,
FROM OUTER SPACE?
JUST WATCH ME, I GUESS, AND
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW IT'S DONE.
LIKE THIS, SEE? FIRST YOU
GOTTA SQUISH IT DOWN A LITTLE
SO YOU CAN GET YOUR
MOUTH AROUND IT.
THEN GRAB HOLD,
OPEN WIDE, AND...
( muffled ) SEE? IT'S EASY!
- SUCH A CUTE GIRL, ISN'T SHE?
WHAT, YOU DON'T THINK SO?
- NO, I DO NOT.
- ( laughs )
- HEY, I THINK YOU MISSED A
SPOT! YOU NEED A NAPKIN?
HAVE YOU EVER USED
A NAPKIN BEFORE?
- GET DOWN!
- ( screaming )
- NO!
- HEY! YOU OKAY?
- I THINK SO, BUT S-SHE...
SHE TRIED TO SAVE ME.
- HEY, GIRL!
- THAT HURT.
- KASHA!
- MIRANDA!
STAY HERE AND
KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN.
- RIGHT. I GOT IT.
- WHERE IS HE?
COME ON, WHERE'S HE
SHOOTING FROM?
- OVER THERE.
- ( gun cocking )
- WELL, I'LL BE DAMNED.
MUST BE A RES OR SOMETHIN'.
- WAIT. UH, OKAY. HE'S GONE.
- THINK I FOUND HER.
- GOOD. CONFIRM.
- I'M POSITIVE. THE COMPUTER
TURNED UP A HIT ON OUR SUSPECT
FROM ONE OF THE CITY'S
SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS.
- AN 89% MATCH ON HER FEATURES?
DOESN'T GET MUCH BETTER
THAN THAT.
- THAT'S HER.
THAT'S GOTTA BE HER.
- Integra: LET'S GO.
- Officer: OH, I SEE.
- SO YOU SAY SOMEONE SHOT AT YOU
YESTERDAY, TOO. INTERESTING.
- YEAH, IT'S JUST
ATTEMPTED MURDER.
NOTHIN' TO GET
WORKED UP OVER!
- CALM DOWN, KASHA, IT'S OKAY.
- SAY, I KNOW IT'S A LITTLE
OFF THE SUBJECT HERE,
BUT DIDN'T I SEE YOU ON TV?
- OH, UH, YES.
- WELL, YOU SEEM
LIKE A SMART LADY.
I MEAN, IF SOMEONE
REALLY TRIED TO KILL YOU,
WHY DIDN'T YOU REPORT IT
TO THE POLICE?
- WE DID! YESTERDAY!
BUT THERE'S NO RECORD
OF A REPORT. SEE WE USUALLY...
- I'M TELLIN' YOU, WE DID!
JEEZ! WHAT IS WITH YOU PEOPLE?
- KASHA, PLEASE.
- MOM, I'M...
- OFFICER, ARE...
- EXCUSE ME, BUT I'M
IN THE MIDDLE OF
TAKING A STATEMENT HERE.
IF YOU NEED TO SPEAK WITH
ANY OF THESE PEOPLE,
I'LL HAVE TO ASK YOU
TO WAIT OUTSIDE FOR...
OH! I-I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOU WERE...
MY MISTAKE, MA'AM!
- THAT'S ALL RIGHT, OFFICER.
AT EASE. WE WON'T BE LONG.
WE JUST HAVE A FEW QUESTIONS
WE'D LIKE TO ASK OF THEM.
- I SHOULD WARN YOU,
TWO ATTEMPTS HAVE BEEN
MADE ON THIS WOMAN'S LIFE
IN THE LAST TWO DAYS.
SO JUST TO MAKE YOU AWARE
OF THE DANGER.
- THANK YOU, OFFICER.
YOUR CONCERN IS DULY NOTED.
WE'LL SEND FOR YOU
IF WE NEED YOU.
- UH, YES, MA'AM! UNDERSTOOD!
I'LL BE IN THE HALL
BY THE VENDING MACHINE.
- I AM INTEGRA MARTEL
FROM R.U.C. SECURITY,
AND WITH ME
IS OFFICER SILVIA BAN.
- HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YOU HAVE NO RIGHT TO...
- WE HAVE EVERY RIGHT.
UNDER THE AUTHORITY
GRANTED US BY R.U.C.,
AND IN THE INTEREST OF
COMPANY SECURITY,
WE'RE DETAINING THIS
GIRL ON SUSPICION
OF INDUSTRIAL ESPIONAGE.
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS!
- IN ANY CASE, WE'RE LEAVING.
- WAIT, PLEASE!
WON'T YOU AT LEAST TELL US
WHAT IT IS YOU THINK SHE'S DONE?
- THIS IS A PHOTO
TAKEN OF THE INTRUDER,
SEEN ENTERING ONE OF
OUR COMPANY'S MOST
HIGH-LEVEL SECURITY AREAS.
WE RAN THIS IMAGE
THROUGH A DETAILED ANALYSIS,
HOPING TO NARROW DOWN
THE LIST OF POSSIBLE SUSPECTS.
INITIALLY, OUR COMPUTERS
WERE UNABLE TO GENERATE
ANY POSITIVE MATCHES
AMONG REGISTERED CITIZENS
OR KNOWN CRIMINALS.
- SO SHE'S AN
UNREGISTERED CITIZEN?
- TODAY, HOWEVER,
OUR SEARCH HIT ON A PHOTO
TAKEN BY ONE OF OUR
SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS
OUTSIDE A DEPARTMENT STORE.
I'M SURE YOU CAN SEE
THE RESEMBLANCE FOR YOURSELF.
OUR ANALYSIS SHOWS AN 89% MATCH.
MORE THAN ENOUGH FOR US
TO BRING HER IN FOR QUESTIONING.
SO, MISS MAVERICK,
ARE YOU SATISFIED?
- COME ON, LET'S GO.
- BUT, UH...
- WAS THERE SOMETHING ELSE?
- MAY I ASK YOU
WHEN THIS ALLEGEDLY HAPPENED?
- IF YOUR INTENT IS TO
SUPPLY HER WITH AN ALIBI,
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
WE KNOW BETTER, MS. MAVERICK.
AND AS I EXPLAINED, THE R.U.C.
COMPUTERS CONFIRMED THE MATCH.
THIS EVIDENCE ALONE IS
MORE THAN SUFFICIENT
TO SECURE A CONVICTION.
- BUT, MOM...
- ROY, PLEASE.
HELP ME, ROY.
- THAT'LL BE ALL.
THE REST OF YOU ARE FREE TO GO.
- COME ON.
- NO. NO!
- I SAID MOVE IT!
- I DON'T WANT TO!
- I'M WARNING YOU...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, SIR?
- INTERFERING WITH
A SECURITY OFFICER
IS A HIGHLY PUNISHABLE OFFENSE!
- SHE'S JUST A KID.
HOW ABOUT YOU GO A
LITTLE EASY ON HER?
- ROY.
- SIR, YOU WILL TAKE YOUR HANDS
OFF ME RIGHT NOW.
- ( grunts )
- NO, DON'T!
- DAMN, BRAT!
MAKE ONE MOVE AND I WILL
END YOU! ARE WE CLEAR?
- STOP, SILVIA. THAT'S ENOUGH.
- ( alarm blaring )
- Kasha: WHAT'S THAT?
- SORRY TO INTERRUPT!
BUT EVERYONE NEEDS TO
EVACUATE THE BUILDING RIGHT NOW!
THERE'S A FIRE
ON THE THIRD FLOOR!
- A FIRE?
- COME ON, LET'S MOVE!
- HEY, THAT'S THE MAN!
ROY, HE'S THE ONE
WHO TRIED TO SHOOT US!
- HOW DID SHE...
- SHE CAUGHT THE BULLET
WITH HER BARE HAND!
- ( alarm stops )
- HE'S ONE of NEUMANN'S BOYS.
- YOU MEAN HE'S FROM
ANOTHER AGENCY?
THEY WERE TRYING TO KILL MOM?
- YEAH. LOOKS THAT WAY.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- IT'S NOT HER.
WE MADE A MISTAKE!
- ( phone beeping)
- THIS BETTER BE IMPORTANT.
- Celica: I, UH, I HAVE
SOMETHING HERE.
SORRY, IT CAN'T WAIT.
WE RAN SOME
FURTHER IMAGE ANALYSIS,
AND THE COMPUTER HAS
CONFIRMED THAT YOUR SUSPECT
DOES NOT MATCH THE INTRUDER.
I REPEAT. YOUR SUSPECT DOES NOT
MATCH THE INTRUDER!
- OH, AND I'LL HAVE
A TALK WITH AXELA
ABOUT BEING MORE CAREFUL!
- BUT IT WASN'T ME, IT WAS
A PROCESSING ERROR! I SWEAR!
- UH-HUH, LIKELY STORY.
BLAME IT ON THE EQUIPMENT!
- SORRY FOR THE INCONVENIENCE.
THE GIRL HAS BEEN CLEARED
OF ANY AND ALL CHARGES.
- DID I MISS SOMETHING?
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
- LIKE I SAID,
YOU ARE FREE TO GO.
NOW THEN, IF YOU DON'T MIND,
WE'LL BE DOING THE SAME.
BUT FOR YOUR OWN GOOD,
I WOULD REMIND YOU
THAT SHE IS STILL
AN UNREGISTERED CITIZEN.
UNLESS YOU INTEND TO
ASSUME LEGAL GUARDIANSHIP,
THE LAW STIPULATES THAT
YOU MUST TURN HER OVER
TO THE PROPER AUTHORITIES.
IT'S VERY CLEAR ON THIS POINT.
- BUT, SHE...
- ROY?
- IS THAT YOUR INTENTION?
- NO, THE GIRL'S NOT MY PROBLEM.
- IN THAT CASE, AN OFFICIAL
FROM THE WELFARE DEPARTMENT
WILL BE BY TO PICK UP
FROM YOUR HOME TOMORROW.
- ROY?
- ( music playing )
- UH, I, UH...
- LOOK, FORGET IT, KID.
JUST GO ON BACK TO MIRANDA'S
AND GET SOME SLEEP.
- Man: DON'T WORRY,
OUR OFFICE WILL SEE TO
IT SHE'S TAKEN CARE OF.
SHE'S IN GOOD HANDS.
- RIGHT. YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET GOING.
- WHAT DID WE DO?
- HOW COULD WE... I MEAN,
THAT GIRL SAVED MY LIFE, MOM.
( sobbing )
- ROY?
- ( tires screeching )
- Man: ( groans ) WHAT THE...
WHAT'S THIS MANIAC THINK
HE'S DOING?
- HOLD UP.
- WELCOME HOME, DEAR!
- LET'S BE CLEAR.
MIRANDA'S YOUR GUARDIAN.
NOT ME. GOT IT?
- OKAY! GOT IT!
- WE'RE GLAD TO HAVE YOU!
- THANK YOU.
- BUT LET'S SET UP SOME RULES,
I'M THE OLDER SISTER, OKAY?
- OKAY!
- NOW THEN,
I SUPPOSE THE FIRST THING WE
NEED TO DO IS GIVE YOU A NAME.
ROY?
- UH...
SOLTY.
- SOLTY?
- DON'T YOU THINK
THAT'S A LITTLE ODD?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT KINDA HAS A RING TO IT.
- SOLTY.
SOLTY!
THAT'S ME!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Solty: MY CHERISHED FIRST DAY.
THE DAY I FIRST MET YOU.
NEXT TIME, "THE GIRL IN BLUE."
WHO ARE YOU?