- Computerized voice: C.R.W.
START UP VOLTAGE IS CONFIRMED.
READY TO INITIATE
NEURAL INTERFACE.
AWAITING YOUR NEXT ORDER.
- ENGAGE.
- ACKNOWLEDGED.
- Yuto: ROY! MIRANDA!
DOES ANYONE KNOW WHAT'S GOING
DOWN AT THE R.U.C. BUILDING?
- LOOKS LIKE THERE
WAS SOME KIND OF ACCIDENT.
- ACCIDENT?
- YEAH. WAIT, WHO'S THAT GUY
AND WHAT'S HE DOING?
- I'LL FILL YOU IN LATER.
- I GUESS YOU GOT TIRED
OF BEING WATCHED, HUH, BRO?
THE SURVEILLANCE TEAM IS
GONE. I FIGURED YOU DID IT.
- YOU DID TAKE THEM
OUT, DIDN'T YOU?
- IT WASN'T ME.
- AH. SORRY, I DIDN'T TELL
YOU BUT I SAW INTEGRA.
SHE WAS JUST HERE.
- ( gasps )
THERE ARE DOZENS OF THEM.
WE GOT TO MOVE.
- ( all gasp )
- ( gunshots )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- CAPTAIN.
- HMM?
- SIR, WE'VE BEEN OVER THIS
BUILDING FROM TOP TO BOTTOM,
BUT THERE'S NO SIGN OF THEM.
IT'S LIKE THEY VANISHED.
- THEN SEARCH AGAIN. THERE WAS
NO WAY FOR THEM TO GET OUT.
- SIR.
- DAMN. WHERE THE HELL
CAN THEY BE HIDING?
- Andy: DAMN IT. WE DIDN'T
EVEN GET TO SIT DOWN
AND IT'S BACK TO THE SEWERS.
- Larry: GIVE IT A REST.
- SOLTY'S GOING TO BE
ALL RIGHT, ISN'T SHE ROY?
- I HOPE SO. JOSEPH.
- YOU ARE GOING TO BE
ABLE TO FIX HER, RIGHT?
- YEP.
- UH, WHERE YOU
TAKING US, GRAMPS?
- JUST FOLLOW ME, KIDDO.
- ARGH, I AM SO SICK
OF YOU, OLD GUYS.
- SO, WERE YOU SERIOUS WHEN
YOU SAID OUR ANCESTORS
MOVED TO THIS PLANET?
- I KNOW IT MUST BE HARD
FOR YOU TO BELIEVE,
BUT, IT'S THE ABSOLUTE TRUTH.
IF YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO FIND THE
EVIDENCE EVERYWHERE IN THE CITY.
- YOUNG LADY, DO YOU KNOW
HOW THIS CITY WAS FOUNDED?
- OH, I . WELL, UH...
- HE MEANS KASHA.
- WELL, ONE TIME
IN HISTORY CLASS,
MY TEACHER TOLD US THAT OUR
ANCESTORS CAME TO THIS LAND FROM
ANOTHER CITY A LONG TIME
AGO AND BUILT THIS ONE.
- YOUR TEACHER TOLD YOU, EH?
- MMM-HMM.
- AND JUST WHERE IS THIS CITY
OUR ANCESTORS WERE SUPPOSED
TO HAVE COME FROM?
- UH...
- WHAT'S IT CALLED?
HOW COME WE NEVER
HEAR ABOUT IT, ANYMORE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVEN'T LEARNED THAT YET.
- RIGHT AND YOU
NEVER WILL, EITHER.
BECAUSE IT DOESN'T EXIST.
- WHAT?
- THINK ABOUT THIS
UNDERGROUND CITY HERE.
IF OUR ANCESTORS
CAME FROM
SOME PLACE ELSE ON THIS PLANET,
WHY WOULD THEY BUILD
A PLACE LIKE THIS?
WHAT USE COULD THEY
POSSIBLY HAVE HAD FOR A CITY
BUILT UNDER THE EARTH?
- UH, MAYBE THEY BUILT IT
TO PROTECT THEMSELVES
FROM SOMETHING?
- SUCH AS.
- UH, I DON'T KNOW.
- MAYBE IT'LL MAKE SENSE
IF YOU TRY THINKING
ABOUT IT LIKE THIS.
HUMAN BEINGS NEED
AIR TO BREATHE.
WHEN PEOPLE FIRST
ARRIVED ON THIS PLANET,
IT HAD NO VIABLE ATMOSPHERE.
SO, THEY NEEDED A
SECURE PLACE TO LIVE
UNTIL ONE COULD BE ESTABLISHED.
THE UNDERGROUND
CITY IS THAT PLACE.
ONCE, THE AURORA
SHELL WAS ERECTED,
AND THE ATMOSPHERE
WAS STABILIZED,
THE PEOPLE MOVED BACK
TO THE SURFACE.
AS MORE AND MORE FOLKS LEFT FOR
THE SUNLIGHT AND OPEN SPACES,
THE UNDERGROUND
CITY WAS DISCARDED,
AND IT'S ORIGINAL
PURPOSE WAS FORGOTTEN.
- I'LL BUY IT,
BUT ONLY UP TO A POINT.
- BUT WHAT GOOD
DOES THIS DO US NOW?
THE ENTIRE UNDERGROUND CITY
WAS BUILT BY CANNIBALIZING
THE TECHNOLOGY
OF THE ORIGINAL SHIP
THE COLONISTS LANDED IN.
- ( gasping )
- THIS CHAMBER WAS ACTUALLY
A COMPLETE SECTION
OF THE ORIGINAL SHIP.
- WHOA!
- Andy: AND I THOUGHT
I KNEW THE UNDERGROUND.
- YOU THINK YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO FIX HER WITH THIS STUFF?
- THIS EQUIPMENT
WAS ORIGINALLY USED
TO REPAIR THE SHIP'S COMPONENTS
AND PARALLEL
PROCESSING CIRCUITS.
SOLTY'S SYSTEMS ARE SO COMPLEX,
THEY CAN ONLY BE REPAIRED
BY THE SAME TECHNOLOGY.
- DID YOU SAY THE
SAME TECHNOLOGY?
- YES, SIR. SOLTY WAS
CONSTRUCTED USING THE SAME
A.I. TECHNOLOGY THAT
WAS USED TO BUILD THIS SHIP.
- WHOA.
- Girl: HEY, LADY.
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- HUH? OH, NO, NOTHING,
I'M FINE. THANKS, ANYWAY.
- THAT'S GOOD. I'M GLAD.
- YOU BE CAREFUL NOW, OKAY?
- OKAY.
- IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'VE MADE A FRIEND.
YOU KNOW, THAT LITTLE GIRL
WILL NEVER HAVE A HOME
WHERE THE SUN SHINES, BECAUSE
SHE'S AN UNREGISTERED CITIZEN.
SHE'LL NEVER HAVE AN
EDUCATION OR A DECENT JOB.
NONE OF THESE KIDS WILL EVER
HAVE ANY OF THE BENEFITS
YOU TAKE FOR GRANTED. ROSE AND
ANDY AND I HAVE SPENT OUR LIVES
FIGHTING FOR THESE KIDS'
FUTURES. BUT I DON'T SUPPOSE
A FORMER R.U.C. EMPLOYEE
CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
- YOU'RE MISTAKEN. YOU SEE,
I USED TO BE ONE OF THEM.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
BUT I'M THE ONLY ONE LEFT,
AND IT'S UP TO ME TO
SEE THAT MY FRIENDS
GET THE JUSTICE THEY DESERVE.
- Reporter: THERE HAVE BEEN
FURTHER DEVELOPMENTS,
IN THE ONGOING INVESTIGATION
OF THE R.U.C. MURDER CASE.
ONE OF THE SUSPECTS,
INTEGRA MARTEL,
WAS ARRESTED YESTERDAY,
AFTER FORCING HER WAY
INTO THE R.U.C. BUILDING.
FOLLOWING A VIOLENT STRUGGLE
WITH SECURITY PERSONNEL,
MARTEL WAS CRITICALLY WOUNDED
AND HAS BEEN PLACED IN A
SECURE INTENSIVE CARE FACILITY.
FUGITIVE, AXELA WARRICK,
REMAINS AT LARGE,
AND AUTHORITIES HAVE ISSUED
ARREST WARRANTS,
FOR THE FOLLOWING
FIVE INDIVIDUALS
--SUSPECTED AS HER ACCOMPLICES.
- ( Miranda gasps )
- OH, GREAT. NOW, THE COPS
ARE AFTER US AS WELL
- I'M SCARED.
- IT'S GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT,
HONEY, DON'T WORRY.
- OKAY JOSEPH.
WHAT'S YOUR FRIEND, LYNX,
TRYING TO GAIN BY ALL OF THIS?
AND HOW MUCH
DO YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?
I THINK IT'S TIME YOU START
LAYING YOUR CARDS
OUT ON THE TABLE.
- YES, I THINK IT IS.
BUT IN ORDER TO DO THAT,
FIRST I'LL HAVE TO TELL YOU
HOW THINGS REALLY
WORK IN THIS CITY.
- ( beeps )
- Computerized voice:
MAINTENANCE COMPLETE.
COMMENCING RESUSCITATION.
- I TRUST YOU'RE
FEELING ALL RIGHT, ROSE?
- NOT TOO BAD.
- WE'VE GOT EVERYTHING
READY TO BEGIN.
IT'S ALL UP TO YOU, NOW.
- I'D LIKE TO MEET SOMEONE,
BEFORE WE START.
- AND WHO'S THAT?
- TAKE ME TO MEET OUR ENEMY.
- THIS IS OUR ENEMY.
THIS IS EUNOMIA.
- INCREDIBLE.
- IT'S THE BEATING HEART
OF THE WHOLE CITY,
AND THE CORE COMPUTER
FOR ALL OF R.U.C.
- IT'S CALLED EUNOMIA.
IT'S BEEN THE MASTER
COMPUTER OF THE CITY,
EVER SINCE THE DAYS OF
THE ORIGINAL COLONISTS.
IT HAS ABSOLUTE CONTROL
OF THE CITY'S ENERGY SOURCES,
THE POWER GRID, THE WATER
SUPPLY, YOU NAME IT.
YOU MIGHT CALL IT
THE CITY'S LIFELINE.
- EUNOMIA WAS CHARGED
WITH THE RESPONSIBILITY
OF DOING WHATEVER
WAS NECESSARY
TO KEEP THE HUMAN RACE
FROM EXTINCTION.
INCLUDING CONTROLLING
AND DIRECTING THEIR LIVES.
BUT, OF COURSE,
YOU CAN'T CONTROL PEOPLE
JUST WITH ENERGY AND WATER.
SO, R.U.C. WAS CREATED
TO BE THE CITY'S CENTRAL ENTITY.
R.U.C. IS A SHADOW GOVERNMENT
WITHIN A CORPORATION.
IT ACTS ON EUNOMIA'S BEHALF.
SHAPING AND MANAGING
HUMANITY AND SOCIETY.
EUNOMIA ESTABLISHED THE SYSTEM
OF CITIZEN REGISTRATION
THROUGH R.U.C.
IT IS THE CAUSE OF THE SUFFERING
OF THE UNREGISTERED CITIZENS.
- WHY CREATE SUCH A SYSTEM?
- AS THE POPULATION GREW,
VARIOUS INEQUITIES AROSE
IN ENERGY, IN
FOOD, MEDICINE AND SERVICES.
IT USED THE SYSTEM
TO CONTROL THESE INEQUITIES,
BY GUARANTEEING THAT SUPPLY
WOULD ALWAYS MEET DEMAND.
- THAT'S HORRIBLE.
- PEOPLE ARE PRONE
TO NEGATIVE EMOTIONS.
ENVY, HATE, CRUELTY,
THEY HAVE A DEEP NEED TO
FEEL SUPERIOR TO OTHERS.
BY DELIBERATELY CREATING
A CLASS OF HAVE-NOTS
TO LOOK DOWN ON,
EUNOMIA WAS ABLE TO CONTROL
THE DISCONTENT OF THE HAVES.
- BUT THAT'S ABSURD. THAT'S
THE CAUSE OF ALL THIS PAIN?
- IT DOESN'T STOP THERE.
NOW, EUNOMIA IS TRYING
TO EXTEND ITS CONTROL
--OF HUMANITY.
- HUH?
- AND THIS IS WHAT
IT'S GOING TO USE.
- RESEMBLE.
- ANYONE EQUIPPED WITH ANY
SORT OF RESEMBLE TECHNOLOGY
IS LINKED DIRECTLY TO EUNOMIA.
OF COURSE, THIS HASN'T
BEEN REVEALED TO ANYONE.
- HOLD ON.
IF THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE
SUCH A DEEP, DARK SECRET,
THEN HOW DO YOU KNOW
SO MUCH ABOUT IT?
LIKE BEFORE, WHEN YOU STROLLED
INTO A HIGH SECURITY AREA
THAT NO ONE SHOULD BE
ABLE TO ACCESS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- FOR THE PAST
TWO HUNDRED YEARS,
EVER SINCE THE FIRST SHIP
CAME TO COLONIZE THIS PLANET,
IT HAS BEEN MY DUTY TO
OVERSEE THE GROWTH
OF THE CITY AND ITS PEOPLE.
- ( gasps )
- BUT, IF THAT'S TRUE THEN
THE REGISTRATION SYSTEM...
- IS PARTLY MY DOING, YES.
- AND NOW YOU WANT
TO DESTROY IT? WHY?
- BECAUSE I WAS WRONG.
I MADE A MISTAKE.
WE CAN CHANGE IT, THE TWO OF US.
WE CAN FREE THIS WORLD OF
ITS MACHINE-MADE SHACKLES.
- YOU AND I, TOGETHER CAN DO IT.
- YOU AND I, TOGETHER?
- Andy: SO, WHAT DOES
THIS ASHLEY GUY
THINK HE'S GOING TO DO
WITH THIS EUNOMIA THING?
- TO PUT IT AS
SIMPLY AS POSSIBLE,
I BELIEVE HE WANTS
TO TURN IT OFF.
- ( gasps )
- WAIT, BUT THAT'S JUST CRAZY.
IF HE TAKES THE
WHOLE CITY DOWN,
THEN HE'S GOING
TO GO DOWN WITH IT.
- NEVERTHELESS,
THAT'S WHAT HE'S AFTER.
ASHLEY HAS ALWAYS LOATHED BEING
UNDER THE CONTROL OF A MACHINE,
EVER SINCE THE OLD DAYS.
- SINCE THE OLD DAYS?
- ASHLEY AND I WERE
COLLEAGUES A LONG TIME AGO.
- WHAT THE...
- BUT WE HAD A
PARTING OF THE WAYS.
- ROY, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- I JUST DON'T KNOW, IT'S A
LOT TO SWALLOW, BUT STILL.
- STILL WHAT ?
- BUT STILL IT'S POSSIBLE AND
WE CAN'T SIMPLY LAUGH IT OFF.
- AND I CAN'T SHAKE
THE FEELING,
THAT HE'S NOT GOING TO
BE SATISFIED WITH SIMPLY
TURNING IT OFF.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- MAYBE HE'S PLANNING TO
MAKE HIMSELF A DICTATOR.
- ( sighs ) MAYBE HE IS.
- BUT THERE'S STILL ONE OTHER
THING I CAN'T FIGURE OUT.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- IT'S ROSE.
- ( gasps )
- I CAN'T FIGURE OUT HOW ROSE
FITS INTO THIS WHOLE SCHEME.
- OF COURSE, I KNEW.
I KNEW WHY ROSE WAS NECESSARY.
I KNEW BECAUSE OF THE PROJECT.
THE PROJECT I WAS A PART OF,
AND THAT ROSE REPLACED ME IN.
- ROSE, ARE YOU READY TO GO?
- I TAKE IT THIS IS A MACHINE
THAT ISN'T UNDER
EUNOMIA'S CONTROL.
- ABSOLUTELY NOT. THIS SYSTEM
HAS NO CONNECTION TO EUNOMIA,
BECAUSE I BUILT IT FROM THE
GROUND UP, IN TOTAL SECRECY.
IT TOOK A VERY LONG TIME,
BUT, IN THE END,
I THINK IT WILL BE WORTH IT.
- WHAT IS IT?
- NOTHING, LET'S GET STARTED.
- THE PROJECT I WORKED ON
WAS A RADICAL EFFORT.
AN ATTEMPT TO USE
A PROCEED'S PROCESSING ABILITY,
TO LINK THE MIND DIRECTLY
INTO A COMPUTER.
- Researcher:
BEGINNING INITIAL START UP.
TRANSFER OF BIO
PATTERNS CONFIRMED,
PUPIL CONTRACTION RATIO GREEN,
BRAINWAVE PATTERN GREEN.
INITIATING FIRST CONTACT.
- ( gasps )
- Researcher 2:
FIRST CONTACT STAGE COMPLETE.
- Axela: AND NOW, ROSE HAS
TAKEN MY PLACE IN THE PROGRAM.
JOSEPH'S STORY MADE
EVERYTHING CLEAR TO ME.
ASHLEY WANTED AN INDEPENDENT
COMPUTER TO CHALLENGE EUNOMIA,
BUT HE COULDN'T FIND A MACHINE
THAT COULD MATCH ITS POWER.
PROCEED ABILITY GAVE HIM
A NEW ALTERNATIVE.
A LIVING INTERFACE TO CONNECT
WITH A COMPUTER,
WHICH MEANS
HE'S GOING TO USE ROSE.
- Researcher: PREPARATIONS
FOR FINAL CONTACT COMPLETE.
TRANSFERRING OPERATIONAL
CONTROL TO SUBJECT.
- SEND ME IN.
- Axela: TO HACK INTO
EUNOMIA'S OPERATING SYSTEM.
- INITIATE DIVE.
- ONCE PAST IT'S DEFENSES,
HE CAN BYPASS ITS ARTIFICIAL
INTELLIGENCE SYSTEM,
AND DESTROY
IT'S CORE PROGRAMMING.
SHUT IT DOWN SO THAT EUNOMIA'S
NOTHING BUT USELESS BOX,
THAT HE CONTROLS.
- IT SETS UP FIREWALLS ALMOST
AS FAST AS I CAN BREACH THEM.
WITH THIS KIND OF POWER,
NO WONDER IT CAN
RUN AN ENTIRE CITY.
- Researcher: FIREWALL
NUMBER 127 HAS BEEN BREACHED.
PREPARING TO INSERT TERTIARY
SUB-VIRUS. SHE'S ATTACKING.
- HER SPEED, IT'S INCREDIBLE.
FASTER THAN ANY
ANYTHING I'VE EVER SEEN.
- SO FAR, SO GOOD.
THE QUESTION NOW IS,
WHAT WILL EUNOMIA DO NEXT,
TO DEFEND ITSELF.
WHATEVER YOU DO, I'LL BE READY.
- IT WORKED, YOU'RE OKAY.
- HEY, HOW ARE YOU
FEELING, SOLTY?
- YOU STILL LOOK WEAK.
ARE YOU SURE YOU SHOULD
BE UP AND WALKING?
- Yuto: SHE'S RIGHT.
MAYBE THAT MACHINE HAD
SOME KIND OF SIDE EFFECT.
- WHO ARE YOU PEOPLE?
- QUIT KIDDING AROUND, SOLTY.
YOU'RE SCARING ME.
- SOLTY?
- ( gasps ) GET OUT!
YOU'VE GOT TO GET AWAY
FROM HERE. RIGHT NOW!
- ( screams )
- Woman 1: WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- Woman 2: I DON'T KNOW.
THEY JUST STARTED SCREAMING.
- HUH?
- THEY'VE STOPPED.
- Woman 1: WHAT WAS IT?
- Woman 2: IT'S LIKE THEY ALL
HAD AN ATTACK OF SOME SORT.
- Man: WAIT, LOOK AT THEIR EYES.
- ( grunts )
- ( Woman screams )
- Man: THEY'VE GONE CRAZY.
- ( cars honking )
- ( people screaming )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, SIR?
- STAY AT YOUR STATIONS.
- BUT SIR...
- ( grunting )
- I KNEW YOU'D
TRY THIS, EUNOMIA.
USING RESEMBLE TO TAKE CONTROL.
- ( people screaming )
- DAMN. WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON NOW?
- YOU GUYS LOOKING FOR A FIGHT?
THEN, BRING IT ON.
- NO, YOU DON'T HAVE KILL THEM.
- ( grunts )
- THEY'RE RESEMBLE. DESTROY
ONLY THEIR RESEMBLE PARTS.
- ( gunshot )
- FINE TIME TO BE PICKY.
- THE SHOCK SHOULD
RENDER THEM UNCONSCIOUS.
- WHAT'S MAKING THEM
ACT LIKE THIS?
- EUNOMIA IS USING
A MICROWAVE RADIO SIGNAL
TO TAKE CONTROL THROUGH
THEIR RESEMBLE IMPLANTS.
- AND HOW DO WE
PUT A STOP TO THAT?
- THE TRANSMISSION TOWER.
- ON THE R.U.C. BUILDING.
IF WE CAN DESTROY THE TOWER,
EUNOMIA WON'T BE ABLE
TO BROADCAST ANYMORE.
- YES, SHE'S RIGHT,
THERE'S NO OTHER WAY.
- THERE'S ONLY
ONE WAY I KNOW
TO REACH THAT
TRANSMISSION TOWER.
- Computerized voice: ALL PULSE
AND NEURO-NETWORK CONNECTIONS
HAVE BEEN ESTABLISHED.
- ( gasps )
( crying ) IT HURTS.
OH GOD, IT HURTS.
SYLVIA, CELICA, INTEGRA.
I SWEAR I WON'T FAIL.
I'LL MAKE THAT BASTARD
SUFFER FOR ALL HE'S DONE.
YOU'LL PAY, ASHLEY LYNX.
- WHAT'S THAT? EARTHQUAKE?
- NO.
- THIS JUST KEEPS GETTING
BETTER. WHAT'S HAPPENING NOW?
- MAYBE EUNOMIA
IS ATTACKING AGAIN.
- THE BUILDINGS.
THE WHOLE CITY'S SHAKING.
( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
I DID IT, I GOT IT.
I GOT IT MOVING
( laughs ) I'M COMING FOR YOU.
- ASHLEY, YOU HEAR
ME, I'M COMING!
I'M GOING TO MAKE YOU PAY,
YOU EGOTISTICAL, SON OF A BITCH.
- Computerized voice: SELF
PRESERVATION FUNCTION ACTIVATED.
SAVING FORCED REVIVAL PULSE.
- ( screams )
I'LL HAVE MY REVENGE.
- ( loud explosion )
- ( laughs )
YES.
- ( gasps ) AXELA.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Solty: YOU'VE GOT TO STOP.
- Axela: I CAN'T. I'M SORRY.
- Solty: NEXT TIME,
"THREE GIRLS, THREE INTENTIONS."
WHAT BRINGS YOU HAPPINESS?