- ( Axela laughing )
LOOK AT IT! LOOK AT IT BURN!
BASTARDS! I HATE THEM!
I HATE THEM ALL!
- AXELA.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- SO, YOU'RE GOING
TO R.U.C., HUH?
- WELL, I CAN'T FIX ANYTHING
BY STAYING HERE, CAN I?
BESIDES, IF ROSE REALLY IS
DOING ASHLEY'S DIRTY WORK,
I HAVE TO STOP HER.
I'M HER FATHER.
SHE'S MY RESPONSIBILITY.
- AND SHE'S OURS, TOO.
- WHAT GOOD ARE BIG BROTHERS
IF THEY CAN'T LOOK
AFTER THEIR KID SISTER?
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- BE CAREFUL AND WATCH
EACH OTHER'S BACKS.
OH, AND DON'T DO
ANYTHING STUPID.
- THANKS KASHA. MIRANDA,
TAKE CARE OF THIS BUNCH, OKAY?
- YOU GOT IT, ROY.
- I'M COUNTING
ON YOU, TOO, YUTO.
- RIGHT.
- NOW, FOR THE HARD PART.
JUST HOW ARE WE GOING
TO GET IN THERE? IT'S RISKY,
BUT IF WE SPLIT UP, WE MIGHT
MAKE HARDER TARGETS,
BUT, IF WE GO IN AS A GROUP,
WELL, IF WE GET PINNED DOWN
OR SURROUNDED,
WE WON'T STAND A CHANCE.
- EXCUSE ME.
- HUH?
- WHAT YOU NEED
IS ME, AS A DECOY.
- A DECOY?
- WHAT, DO YOU HAVE
SOMETHING IN MIND?
- YES, YOU'LL HAVE TO
TRUST ME.
- I KNOW I CAN DRAW
THEIR ATTENTION OUTSIDE.
THAT SHOULD GIVE
THE REST OF YOU A CHANCE TO...
- WHAT, ARE YOU CRAZY?
YOU'RE JUST A KID.
WE'RE NOT USING YOU
AS A DECOY, THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
- I THINK YOU'RE
ALL FORGETTING
THAT I'M A TRAINED
MEMBER OF PROCEED.
I AM. I'M SKILLED IN COMBAT
AND I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
IF I SHOW UP AT R.U.C.,
THEY'LL ASSUME I'M THERE
TO AVENGE MY TEAM MATES
AND THEY'LL TRY TO PURSUE ME.
- IT'S NOT A BAD IDEA.
- BUT...
- LOOK, ROY, IF YOU'VE
GOT A BETTER PLAN,
I'D REALLY LOVE TO HEAR IT.
- ALL RIGHT, SO, LET'S SAY
WE GO THROUGH WITH THIS,
DON'T YOU THINK WE SHOULD
AT LEAST SEND SOMEBODY WITH HER?
PROCEED OR NOT,
WE CAN'T LET HER BE A DECOY
BY HERSELF NOW, CAN WE?
- UH, NO, I CAN MANAGE ALONE.
- UM.
- I'LL GO. I'LL DO IT.
- YOU, SOLTY?
- WHAT? YOU DON'T HAVE...
- I'LL GO WITH AXELA.
I CAN HELP HER GET INTO R.U.C.,
IF THAT'S OKAY WITH HER.
- UH, FINE.
- SOLTY.
- SOMEBODY'S GOING TO
HAVE TO DO IT, ROY.
- PLEASE DON'T WORRY, I WON'T
LET ANYTHING HAPPEN TO HER.
SHE'S SAFE WITH ME.
- YOU AND I KNOW, SHE'D MAKE
A HELL OF A BODYGUARD.
- AT THE FIRST SIGN OF TROUBLE,
YOU GET OUT OF THERE.
- I WILL. WELL, AXELA, READY
TO GIVE IT OUR BEST SHOT?
- YEAH, SURE.
- ( laughing )
- SORRY FOR THE DECEPTION,
BUT THE TRUTH IS I HAD TO
USE ALL OF YOU AS MY DECOY.
YOU SEE, IT WAS
THE ONLY WAY
TO GET ME INSIDE THIS
BEAUTIFUL BABY.
- ARE YOU SURE THIS ELEVATOR
WILL TAKE US ALL THE WAY UP
TO THE SURFACE LEVEL?
OKAY, AXELA. ARE YOU
READY TO DO THIS?
- AXELA, ARE YOU...
- FORGIVE ME, SOLTY.
- AXELA.
AXELA, AXELA!
THE CITY, IT'S SHAKING.
- ( laughing )
- AXELA.
- Joseph: SOLTY.
- HUH?
- JUST ONE THING. IF MY
CALCULATIONS ARE CORRECT,
YOUR STRENGTH SHOULD HAVE
RETURNED TO FULL POWER BY NOW.
ALL OF YOUR
ABILITIES ARE ACTIVE.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
WANT TO KNOW.
- MY STRENGTH, THAT'S RIGHT.
- WHY IS EVERYTHING SHAKING?
WHAT'S GOING ON OUT THERE?
- Researcher:
NONE OF YOUR CONCERN.
JUST CONCENTRATE
ON THE TASK AT HAND.
- HOW CAN I WHEN THE WHOLE
DAMN BUILDING IS SHAKING APART?
- THOSE ARE THE OPERATIONS
DIRECTOR'S ORDERS.
- MAN!
THESE GUYS THINK ALL THEY
HAVE TO DO IS MENTION ASHLEY,
AND I'LL BEHAVE
JUST LIKE A TRAINED PET.
WELL, IF THAT'S HOW
THEY WANT TO PLAY,
EXTERNAL MONITORS
1, 2, 3 ON SCREEN.
- ( beeps )
- WHOA, WHAT IS THAT THING?
- WHAT THE HELL
IS CAUSING THESE TREMORS?
- HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
JUST DEAL WITH IT.
- GUYS, UP AHEAD.
- THIS IS NOT GOOD.
- THESE GUYS ARE PISSING ME OFF.
- REMEMBER, DON'T KILL THEM.
THEY'RE ALL BEING MANIPULATED.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- THIS WAY.
- TAKE THIS WITH YOU. I INSIST.
- THAT THING YOU SENT?
- SO, WHAT IS IT?
- AN ACTIVATION KEY
THAT WILL COME IN HANDY.
- YOU NEED TO MAKE IT
TO THE BASEMENT OF R.U.C.
THERE YOU'LL FIND
A SUBSYSTEM ROOM.
ONCE INSIDE, INSERT THE KEY,
AND IT SHOULD DISRUPT
R.U.C.'S MAIN OPERATING
SYSTEM FOR A WHILE.
- WHAT...
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I JUST DON'T GET IT.
A POWERFUL DEVICE LIKE THIS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH IT, OLD MAN?
- WHEN I LEFT R.U.C., I HELPED
MYSELF TO THIS LITTLE ITEM.
WITH HIS AMBITIONS, I THOUGHT
IT MIGHT BE A NECESSARY TOOL
TO USE AGAINST ASHLEY ONE DAY.
- I'M SURPRISED, YOU HAVEN'T
USED THIS KEY BEFORE.
- THERE WAS NO WAY I
COULD STOP HIM BACK THEN,
BUT NOW, WE MIGHT HAVE A CHANCE.
THAT KEY WILL ONLY SHUT DOWN
R.U.C. TEMPORARILY,
BUT, THAT COULD BE JUST ENOUGH
TIME TO CATCH ASHLEY OFF-GUARD.
AT LEAST IT GIVES US
A FIGHTING CHANCE, EH?
- DON'T WORRY,
I'LL PUT IT TO GOOD USE.
- ( laughing )
I'M GOING TO DESTROY IT,
EVERY BIT.
IT'S IRONIC THAT I'M USING
YOUR OWN CREATION
TO OBLITERATE ALL YOUR
HOPES AND DREAMS.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
DO YOU, ASHLEY LYNX?
( gasps )
- AXELA.
- AXELA, I KNOW
IT'S YOU IN THERE.
- SOLTY.
- YOU HAVE TO STOP.
IF YOU DO THIS, LOTS OF
INNOCENT PEOPLE WILL GET HURT.
- BUT HE KILLED MY BEST FRIENDS.
I WON'T LET HIM GET
AWAY WITH MURDER.
- AXELA!
- GET OUT OF THE WAY.
I CAN'T STOP IT.
- ( grunts )
( screams )
( gasps )
- SOLTY. YOU ALWAYS
WERE A RECKLESS ONE.
- ROSE, THANK YOU.
- ( screaming )
- THERE GO OUR
SHOPS. DAMN IT.
WE CAN'T LET THEM
GET ANY CLOSER.
- HOLD THEM BACK. FIRE! FIRE!
- NOW'S YOUR CHANCE.
GET OUT OF THERE! RUN!
- COME ON. LET'S GO.
- YOU? BUT YOU'RE A...
- WAIT, ARE THEY
UNREGISTERED CITIZENS, TOO?
- YES, THEY ARE.
- WHY THEN. WHY
ARE YOU HELPING US?
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
HATED REGISTERED CITIZENS.
- YOU SHOULD ALWAYS LEND A
HAND WHEN SOMEONE IS IN NEED,
AM I RIGHT?
- ( laughs ) GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
- ( machine beeping )
- ( grunting )
- HEY, COME ON, NOW.
WAS THAT REALLY NECESSARY?
- IT IS WITH THESE GUYS.
- HESITATE AND THEY'LL KILL YOU.
DON'T BE A COWARD, YUTO.
- COWARD, HUH? YOU SEEM
TO HAVE FORGOTTEN
WHO RESCUED YOU A
FEW MINUTES AGO.
- OH, THAT WAS YOU,
WASN'T IT? SORRY.
- FORGET IT.
- LET'S JUST GET INTEGRA
OUT OF HERE BEFORE
ANY MORE OF THOSE
GUYS DECIDE TO SHOW UP.
- COME ON, THIS WAY.
QUICKLY! HURRY UP!
- Miranda: KASHA.
- HUH?
( screams )
- MOM, BEHIND YOU.
- GOT THEM.
- ( laughs ) I WANT TO HELP.
( chuckles )
- HONEY, YOU'VE GOT
TO BE MORE CAREFUL.
- MOM, DID YOU SEE?
THIS RIOT GEAR'S GREAT.
ALL I HAD TO DO WAS AIM,
PULL THE TRIGGER AND BOOM.
I TOOK THEM DOWN,
JUST WITH ONE SHOT.
- ( chuckles ) THAT'S MY
DAUGHTER. THE SHARPSHOOTER.
- THEY'RE WEARING DOWN OUR
STRENGTH AND OUR AMMUNITION.
I DON'T KNOW LONG
WE CAN HOLD OUT.
- WELL, THEN,
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO MAKE EVERY
SHOT COUNT UNTIL THIS IS OVER.
- ( people screaming )
- WHAT, WHAT'S THAT?
- OH, NO THOSE, TOO?
- THEY'RE BEING CONTROLLED?
- HUH? ROSE.
- I WAS WATCHING.
SO, YOU CAN FLY?
- YES, AFTER JOSEPH
REPAIRED ME.
- SO, WHO'S BEHIND
THE CONTROLS OF THAT THING?
- AXELA. I'VE BEEN
TRYING TO TALK TO HER.
- I'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO STOP HER SOMEHOW.
- I SEE, AXELA, HUH?
- ROSE ANDERSON.
- ROSE, WAIT.
- SORRY, AXELA, IT'S
NOTHING PERSONAL
BUT I'VE GOT TO PUT AN
END TO THIS, RIGHT NOW.
- NO, THAT'S NOT THE WAY.
- ( grunting )
- COME ON, TODAY, ANDY.
- THEY DON'T STOP.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- ANDY, LOOKOUT!
- LARRY!
- ( screams )
- IT'S OPEN. INSIDE.
- LARRY, ARE YOU OKAY?
- OH, NO YOU DON'T. I AM SO SICK
OF YOU GUYS GETTING IN OUR WAY.
- DAMN IT!
- LARRY!
- I'M COUNTING ON YOU. DO ME
A FAVOR AND GO END THIS THING,
OKAY, LITTLE BROTHER?
- NO, LARRY. LARRY!
- HEY, ROY?
TAKE GOOD CARE OF HIM.
- ALL RIGHT, COME ON,
YOU BASTARDS.
I'M SICK OF PLAYING NICE.
- ( screaming )
- ( Andy crying )
LARRY.
- ( elevator bell rings )
- WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
- IT'S ROBOTS, HUH? GOOD,
WE DON'T HAVE TO HOLD BACK.
- DAMN RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
- PLEASE STOP IT, ROSE.
YOU HAVE TO.
- YOU BETTER GET
OUT OF HERE, SOLTY.
( gasps )
- SOLTY?
- Computerized voice: ENERGY
CHARGE, THIRTY-SEVEN PERCENT.
- FIRE.
- INSUFFICIENT POWER.
- YOU HEARD ME, FIRE!
- FIRING.
- ( grunts ) STOP GETTING
IN MY WAY.
- NO, I WON'T.
I'M NOT GOING TO STAND BY
AND LET YOU SHOOT AXELA.
- WHAT, HAVE YOU LOST YOUR MIND?
IF YOU DON'T BACK DOWN THEN
I'LL BE FORCED TO KILL YOU, TOO.
- ( gasps ) IF YOU
REALLY MEAN THAT,
THEN I HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO STOP YOU.
- ( screams )
- Computerized voice:
RECHARGING COMMENCING.
CHARGE AT 2, 2.5, 3, 3.5...
- WELL, ROSE, I KNOW YOU'RE
NOT THE ONE WHO'S RESPONSIBLE.
BUT TWO OF MY BEST
FRIENDS ARE GONE.
SYLVIA AND CELICA
ARE GONE FOREVER.
- Computerized voice:
6, 6.5, 7, 7.5...
- BUT IF IT MEANS,
I HAVE TO DESTROY YOU
TO GET TO ASHLEY THEN,
THEN SO BE IT.
- ROSE, WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- DON'T YOU GET IT?
WE'VE GOT TO STOP HER BEFORE
SHE CAUSES ANY MORE DAMAGE.
- BUT LIKE THIS? THERE'S
GOT TO BE ANOTHER WAY.
- IT'S THE SAFEST WAY.
I CAN END THIS WITH ONE SHOT.
- MOVE OR I'LL TAKE
YOU DOWN, TOO.
- STOP BEING SO STUBBORN.
- IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
- YOU CAN'T KILL AXELA.
- Rose: I DON'T WANT TO.
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO,
BUT IT'S NECESSARY.
THERE HAVE BEEN TOO
MANY VICTIMS ALREADY.
I WON'T LET THERE BE
ANY MORE. NO ONE, NONE.
SYLVIA AND CELICA, THEY'RE BOTH
DEAD AND INTEGRA, SHE'S...
- ( gasps )
- Rose: IT'S TOO LATE
TO TURN BACK NOW.
- NO, IT'S NOT, ROSE.
- IF I STOP NOW,
THEIR SACRIFICES WOULD
HAVE BEEN MADE IN VAIN.
- AND THAT'S WHY
I HAVE TO DO THIS.
- WHY DO YOU FEEL LIKE THIS?
- IT'S FOR THE GOOD OF EVERYONE.
IF I DO NOTHING, IT,
IT'LL NEVER COME TRUE.
- WHAT, WHAT, ROSE?
- I'VE ALWAYS HATED THE
CITIZEN REGISTRATION SYSTEM.
HATED IT EVEN
WHEN I WAS A CHILD.
I ALWAYS HOPED
IT WOULD FALL APART,
THEN IT WOULDN'T MATTER WHO
LIVED ABOVE AND WHO LIVED BELOW.
BUT I, I WAS A KID,
SO NO ONE TOOK ME SERIOUSLY.
THEY'D SORT OF
SMILE AND SAY
"THAT'S A NICE FAIRY
TALE, SWEETIE."
BUT ASHLEY, HE WAS DIFFERENT.
HE LISTENED TO EVERYTHING
I HAD TO SAY AND SAID
HE BELIEVED IN ME.
SO, YOU SEE, I'VE GOT
TO HELP ASHLEY! I'VE GOT TO.
- SO, THAT OUR DREAM
CAN COME TRUE.
- BUT KILLING IS WRONG.
- IF I WANT TO REACH OUR GOAL,
WE HAVE TO CLOSE OUR
EYES TO A FEW SACRIFICES.
- IF THAT'S THE WAY YOU
REALLY FEEL, ROSE,
THEN WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
A GOOD DREAM SHOULDN'T
MAKE YOU CRY.
IT SHOULDN'T MAKE
YOU DO BAD THINGS
TO THE ONES YOU CARE ABOUT.
IT'S JUST NOT RIGHT, ROSE.
- LIFE IS PAINFUL, SOLTY.
THAT'S JUST HOW IT IS.
- THAT'S AN EXCUSE.
IT ISN'T ALWAYS THAT WAY.
- GROW UP. IT'S HOW
THE ADULT WORLD WORKS.
- DON'T BE AN ADULT, ESPECIALLY
IF IT MAKES YOU LIKE THIS.
JUST BE YOURSELF. BE THE ROSE,
WE ALL KNOW AND LOVE.
I'M SURROUNDED BY WONDERFUL
PEOPLE WHO I REALLY CARE FOR
AND THEY'RE REALLY GOOD TO ME,
AND I LOVE TO COOK, BECAUSE
IT SEEMS TO MAKE THEM HAPPY.
AND SEEING THE SMILES
ON THEIR HAPPY FACES...
WELL, THAT'S ALL
THAT I'LL EVER NEED.
I'VE GOT A GOOD LIFE AND I HOPE
IT'LL CONTINUE TO BE LIKE THAT.
AND OF COURSE,
ONE OF THE PEOPLE
WHO MAKES MY LIFE
SO WONDERFUL, IS YOU.
- HUH?
- ( beeping )
- AND AXELA, I LOVE YOU, TOO.
- ( gasps )
- I LOVE COOKING WITH YOU,
OR EVEN JUST SITTING
AROUND AND TALKING.
IT WOULD BE SO NICE IF ALL
OF US COULD GET TOGETHER
AND HAVE FUN LIKE THAT AGAIN.
- AND THAT'S, THAT'S MY DREAM.
- YOURS, BUT THAT DREAM IS...
- THE SAME ONE THAT YOU WANT.
EVERYONE COMING TOGETHER.
THAT'S IT, ISN'T IT, ROSE?
- ( gasps )
- I KNOW IT'S BEEN HARD
BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT NOW.
DON'T FEEL BAD, OKAY?
EVERYONE MAKES MISTAKES.
OH, ROSE, WELCOME BACK.
- ( both crying )
- ( crying )
- Computerized voice: CHARGE
COMPLETE. WEAPONS AT FULL POWER.
INITIATING FIRING SEQUENCE.
- THAT'S ENOUGH, ABORT.
- ERROR. INITIATING
FIRING SEQUENCE.
- YOU CAN'T. ABORT.
- RELEASING SAFETY.
ACKNOWLEDGED.
- ( gasps ) STOP.
- ABORT. THAT'S AN ORDER, NOW!
- FIRING.
- NO. GET AWAY!
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
- ARE WE SAFE NOW, MOM?
- LOOKS LIKE IT.
- NO. NOT YET.
- GREAT. DO THOSE THINGS
EVER GIVE UP?
- ( grunts )
- HEY, THEY STOPPED.
- WELL, IS IT OVER?
- GUESS SO.
- GOOD.
THEN LET'S GET THE
HELL OUT OF HERE.
THERE'S NO REASON
TO STICK AROUND NOW.
ANDY, I'M SURE HE'S FINE.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- HUH?
- COME ON.
- HOW WOULD YOU...
YOU'RE RIGHT, OLD MAN.
I GUESS, IT IS MY BIG
BROTHER WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- ATTABOY.
- COME ON, LET'S MOVE.
- LET'S FIND ROSE
AND GET OUT OF HERE.
( grunts )
( groans )
- TRESPASSING IS A CRIME,
MR. REVANT.
AH, DAMN JOSEPH. IT HAD TO BE.
EUNOMIA CAN'T BE SHUT DOWN
BY THE SUBSYSTEM ALONE.
HE'S THE ONLY ONE WHO WOULD
KNOW HOW TO DO SO.
I SHOULD HAVE MADE SURE
HE WAS DEAD LONG AGO.
- ( groans )
- I MUST ADMIT, I'M SURPRISED.
I NEVER THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE THE
ONE WHO'D STOP EUNOMIA FOR ME.
SO HERE'S MY DILEMMA.
SHOULD I THANK YOU
FOR HELPING ME,
OR KILL YOU FOR GETTING
IN MY WAY?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Roy: IS THAT
WHAT YOU REALLY WANT?
- Ashley: THAT? IT IS MY
GRANDEST WISH IN LIFE.
- Rose: NEXT TIME,
"FAREWELL MESSAGE."
- Solty: LET'S KEEP OUR PROMISE.