- Joseph: IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
THERE'S NOTHING
YOU COULD HAVE DONE.
- DO YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
WHY THIS HAPPENED?
- SADLY, I DO.
- PLEASE, TELL ME.
- YOU SEE...
WILL, HE...
HE RAN OUT OF TIME.
- AND YOU STILL HAD SOLTY,
YOU BASTARD!
- THAT HURT.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- WILL HAD A
TROUBLED CHILDHOOD.
HIS PARENTS ABANDONED HIM
WHEN HE WAS ONLY FOUR.
BY THE TIME HE REALIZED
THEY WERE GONE,
HE'D BEEN WANDERING
THE STREETS FOR DAYS.
IT'S A MIRACLE HE
SURVIVED EVEN THAT.
MUCH LESS THE BLAST FALL.
- ( explosion )
- Joseph: WILL TEETERED ON THE
BRINK OF LIFE AND DEATH,
BUT SOMEHOW HE
FOUGHT THROUGH IT.
WHAT ACTUALLY SAVED HIM
WAS RESEMBLE TECHNOLOGY,
WHICH AT THE TIME WAS STILL IN
ITS EARLY STAGES OF DEVELOPMENT.
UNFORTUNATELY, HIS APPOINTED
PHYSICIAN WAS A CORRUPT MAN,
MORE INTERESTED IN
THE VICTIMS' CLAIMS
PAID OUT BY THE CITY THAN
IN THE VICTIMS THEMSELVES.
HE USED INFERIOR PARTS,
AND PROVIDED ONLY THE BARE
MINIMUM OF TREATMENT.
AS A RESULT, WILL'S BODY BEGAN
TO DETERIORATE INTERNALLY.
BEFORE HE EVEN KNEW
THERE WAS A PROBLEM,
IT WAS ALREADY TOO LATE.
- SO WILL KNEW THIS WAS COMING
ALL THIS TIME?
HE KNEW HE WAS GOING TO DIE?
YOU BOTH DID?
- YES, WE BOTH DID.
- THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU...
- I GAVE UP ON THIS WORLD
A LONG TIME AGO.
I'M ONLY A SPECTATOR NOW.
IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
- BUT, STILL,
THAT'S NO REASON TO...
- WILL WANDERED INTO THE DESERT
AND FOUND MY HOUSE.
HIS DECISION TO STAY HERE
WAS HIS OWN.
PERHAPS HE LIKED IT HERE
BECAUSE I KEPT TO MYSELF,
OR MAYBE HE JUST ENJOYED
THE ISOLATION OF THIS PLACE.
IN ANY CASE, I'M REMINDED
OF A CONVERSATION WE HAD.
- DID I EVER TELL YOU, GRAMPS,
ABOUT THAT DAY?
ABOUT THE GLOWING SNOW
I SAW FALLING ON THE CITY?
- THE SNOW WAS GLOWING?
- YEAH. YEAH IT WAS.
IT'S A SIGHT I'LL NEVER FORGET.
THE BLAST FALL. IT WAS
THE WORST DAY OF MY LIFE.
BUT THE PART I REMEMBER,
IT'S LAYING THERE, QUIETLY,
WATCHING THE SNOW.
IT WAS SO BEAUTIFUL, MAGICAL.
I KNEW SOMETHING TERRIBLE
HAD HAPPENED,
BUT IN THAT MOMENT,
NOTHING ELSE MATTERED.
CAUSE MY EYES WERE FILLED WITH
A MILLION FALLING LIGHTS.
- SO IS THAT IT? YOU'RE
BUILDING THIS PLANE
SO YOU CAN SEE THIS
GLOWING SNOW AGAIN?
- ( chuckles ) NO.
THAT'S JUST CRAZY.
I'D DIE BEFORE
I EVER GOT HIGH ENOUGH.
- OKAY, THEN WHY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS,
MAYBE I JUST WANT TO FEEL
THAT PEACE AGAIN.
LIKE THE WAY I FELT WHEN
I WAS WATCHING THAT SNOW.
I JUST WANT TO BELIEVE
THAT THE WORLD IS BEAUTIFUL.
- LIKE I SAID, I AM ONLY
A SPECTATOR IN THIS LIFE.
I DON'T CONCERN MYSELF WITH
THE BUSINESS OF OTHERS.
WHATEVER IT IS YOU DECIDE
TO DO FROM HERE,
STAY OR GO, IT'S YOUR CHOICE,
AND YOURS ALONE.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- YOU CLEANED UP. GOOD.
I TAKE IT THIS MEANS
YOU'RE FEELING BETTER?
- YEP. EXCEPT FOR THE
SORE FACE, THAT IS.
YOU PACK A MEAN PUNCH.
- YEAH, WELL, I THINK IT HURT
ME MORE THAN IT DID YOU.
- JUST LIKE OLD TIMES, HUH?
HOW LONG'S IT BEEN, MIRANDA?
- WELL, IT'S HARD TO SAY REALLY.
YOU WERE JUST STARTING
OUT AS A HUNTER THEN.
- THAT'S RIGHT. YOU HAD TO KNOCK
ME BACK IN LINE THEN, TOO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'D DO
WITHOUT YOU, MIRANDA.
- HAVE YOU MADE UP YOUR MIND?
- YEAH. I'VE COME TO MY SENSES.
- ( keyboard clacking )
- THEY STILL HAVEN'T FOUND HER.
- WHAT HAVE WE HERE?
OH, A MISSING PERSONS
BULLETIN BOARD?
YOU'RE STILL SEARCHING FOR
YOUR PARENTS AREN'T YOU?
FOUND ANY NEW LEADS?
- HEY. YOU CAN CHECK YOUR
EMAIL LATER. WE'VE GOTTA GO.
- UH, RIGHT.
- YEAH, OKAY.
DON'T WORRY, AXELA. I DON'T
HAVE A PROBLEM WITH IT.
YOUR SECRET'S SAFE WITH ME.
I WON'T TELL ANYBODY.
- THANKS, CELICA.
I APPRECIATE IT.
- BUT IN EXCHANGE
FOR MY SILENCE,
DINNER IS ON YOU TONIGHT.
OKAY? GOOD. IT'S A DEAL.
- WHAT?
- NOW WHERE DID SHE GO?
ARE YOU GOING TO
REPAIR THE PLANE?
- YES.
- AND JUST WHY WOULD
YOU DO THAT?
IS THIS FOR WILL?
- I'M NOT REALLY SURE, I GUESS.
I JUST KNOW THAT IT'S
SOMETHING I HAVE TO DO.
- ( sighs )
WELL, THAT'S THE FRAME
FOR THE FUSELAGE.
IT SUPPORTS THE
ENTIRE STRUCTURE.
UNLESS YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
DOING, IF YOU ALTER THE SHAPE,
IT MAY NOT BE ABLE
TO BEAR THE LOAD.
YOU UNDERSTAND THE PRINCIPLES
INVOLVED, CORRECT?
BASIC AERODYNAMICS, FOR A PLANE
TO FLY, IT NEEDS TO PRODUCE
ENOUGH LIFT AND THRUST TO
OVERCOME GRAVITY AND DRAG.
TO HANDLE THE ASSOCIATED STRESS,
THE STRUCTURE OF THE AIRFRAME
NEEDS TO BE
PRECISELY CALCULATED.
IT NEEDS TO BE STURDY,
AND AS LIGHTWEIGHT AS POSSIBLE.
- UM. OH OKAY.
- WILL'S DESIGN SKETCHES
SHOULD BE ON THE
WORKBENCH OVER THERE.
I SUGGEST YOU FAMILIARIZE
YOURSELF WITH THEM.
TRUST ME, IT WILL
BE MUCH EASIER
THAN TRYING TO BUILD
THIS FROM SCRATCH.
- RIGHT. I'LL DO THAT.
THANK YOU.
- OH, IT'S NOTHING. JUST
AN OLD MAN'S RAMBLINGS.
SO MANY OF US HAVE PASTS
WE'D JUST AS SOON FORGET.
BUT THE WEIGHT OF OUR SINS
IS TOO GREAT TO CAST ASIDE.
YOURS AND MINE, BOTH.
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE
SERIOUSLY PLANNING
TO GO THROUGH WITH THIS?
YOU KNOW THE RISKS INVOLVED.
THE CHANCES OF A BACKFIRE
ARE TOO GREAT.
HOW COULD YOU PERSIST?
THEN THERE'S NOTHING ELSE
I CAN DO TO STOP YOU.
I WALKED AWAY FROM YOU THAT DAY,
THE MOMENT OF MY
GREATEST FAILURE.
AND I NEVER LOOKED BACK.
I CHOSE TO BECOME AN
OBSERVER, BUT NOT YOU.
YOUR BLIND AMBITION
KNOWS NO END, ASHLEY.
- Integra: DIRECTOR.
I THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE TO KNOW,
WE'VE MADE SOME PROGRESS IN
THE CLOCK TOWER INVESTIGATION.
IT SEEMS OUR SUSPECT,
JEREMY KOLBEL,
WAS IN FACT ACTING ALONE.
AND THE EXTENT OF THE DAMAGE,
COMPARED TO THE AURORA WAVE
POTENTIAL WAS APPROXIMATELY...
- YOU CAN SPARE ME
THE DETAILS FOR NOW.
I TRUST YOUR TEAM HAS
EVERYTHING WELL IN HAND.
ONCE YOUR REPORT
HAS BEEN FINALIZED,
I'LL BE HAPPY TO READ IT.
IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU HAVE YOUR ORDERS.
HOW'S IT LOOKING?
SHE'S SUPERIOR TO AXELA IN EVERY
WAY, JUST AS I ANTICIPATED.
IT'S TAKEN A LONG TIME,
BUT IT SEEMS I'LL FINALLY
BE FREE OF YOUR CURSE.
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- SILVIA, I HAVE A QUESTION.
- HMM? WHAT IS IT?
- YEAH, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- DON'T YOU HAVE A REPORT
TO WRITE? GET TO WORK!
- YEAH, YEAH.
- DID IT SEEM LIKE THE
OPERATIONS DIRECTOR
WAS ACTING A BIT STRANGE?
- NO. I DON'T KNOW.
STRANGE HOW?
- I'M NOT REALLY SURE.
I CAN'T QUITE PUT
A FINGER ON IT.
- HE SEEMED THE SAME
AS ALWAYS, I GUESS.
I MEAN, MAYBE HE
WAS A LITTLE ABRUPT,
BUT THAT'S COMPLETELY
UNDERSTANDABLE.
HE'S HAD HIS HANDS FULL LATELY.
- Celica: MAYBE HE
WAS UPSET BECAUSE
HE GOT IN A FIGHT WITH
HIS GIRLFRIEND.
I HEAR SOMEONE SPOTTED HIM
ON A DATE NOT TO LONG AGO.
- Silvia: SHUT UP AND
GET BACK TO WORK.
- FINE.
- SO NOTHING SEEMED UNUSUAL?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
- AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
AS LONG AS I GET PAID,
HE CAN DO WHATEVER HE WANTS.
- UH?
- UH.
- ( computer bleeps )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- HERE. IT'S EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN ABLE TO PUT TOGETHER
SO FAR ON SOLTY'S WHEREABOUTS.
- YEAH, GOOD.
THANKS, MIRANDA.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT. YOU CAN
THANK ME WHEN YOU GET BACK.
- LOOK, ROY, IF YOU'RE
GOING OUT TO FIND SOLTY,
TAKE ME WITH YOU.
- I'M DOING THIS ALONE.
- BUT...
- LISTEN YUTO, SORRY.
BUT THIS IS SOMETHING
I HAVE TO DO ON MY OWN.
- THEN GET GOING, WILL YOU?
- KASHA...
- STOP WASTING TIME
AND GO FIND HER.
MOVE IT!
- OKAY. I'M GOING, I'M GOING.
- WHAT TOOK HIM SO LONG?
STUPID.
- THANK GOODNESS. IT'S NOT
NEARLY AS BAD AS I THOUGHT.
I SHOULD HAVE THIS BACK IN
WORKING CONDITION IN NO TIME.
- ♪ WALKING AWAY ♪
♪ AND YOU WILL STAY ♪
♪ THE PASSING DAYS CONTINUING ♪
♪ SLIPPING AWAY ♪
♪ BUT DON'T BE AFRAID ♪
♪ READY OR NOT,
WE'LL MEET AGAIN ♪
♪ I GO, YOU GO, THE SAME
DIRECTION WE WILL CHOOSE ♪
♪ YOU GOT IT? ♪
♪ HEADING ON OUR FUTURE NOW ♪
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( machine beeping )
- LINES 42, 42 AND 49
THROUGH 66 ARE IN THE RED.
SEVEN MORE ARE
APPROACHING CRITICAL.
- HEART RATE AND RESPIRATION
RISING RAPIDLY.
- STRESS CO-EFFICIENT RISING.
WE'RE SEEING SIGNS OF REJECTION.
- PUPILS DILATED.
CONTROL SPEED DECREASING.
- THIS IS AS FAR AS SHE CAN GO.
WE CAN'T PUSH HER ANYMORE, SIR.
- WELL, THEN THAT SETTLES IT.
- ( gasping )
- HEY SOLTY, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
ISN'T THE VIEW AMAZING?
- YEAH. IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
- I JUST WANT TO BELIEVE
THAT THE WORLD IS BEAUTIFUL.
ANYWAY, MY NAME'S WILL.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
BUT IF YOU'RE NOT HAPPY
WITH WHAT YOU DO HAVE,
WELL THEN THE CURE
FOR THAT IS SIMPLE.
YOU JUST HAVE TO
THROW IT ALL AWAY.
THIS IS THE PERFECT PLACE
TO LET IT ALL GO.
WHY'S THAT SO SURPRISING?
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS THAT
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU?
BUT BELIEVE ME WHEN I SAY THIS,
I WAS HALF SERIOUS, TOO.
- Solty: FLY!
- Will: WELL, HAVE YOU DECIDED
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO YET?
COME ON, LET'S HEAR IT.
- YOU KNOW I REALLY
LOVED YOU, WILL.
MORE THAN YOU COULD
EVER IMAGINE.
- I'M HALF KIDDING.
GOTCHA.
YOU KNEW ALL ALONG,
DIDN'T YOU, WILL?
ABOUT YOUR HEALTH.
THAT MUST HAVE SO BEEN HARD.
WAS IT PAINFUL? DID IT HURT?
- I MADE MY CHOICE
A LONG TIME AGO.
- HUH?
ALL THE PAIN,
ALL THE FRUSTRATION,
I JUST DECIDED TO
THROW IT ALL AWAY.
- BUT WHY?
- CAUSE I REALIZED I HAD BECOME
INCAPABLE OF LAUGHING.
AND SINCE I WAS GOING TO
LIVE A SHORT LIFE,
I WANTED THAT LIFE TO BE
FILLED WITH LAUGHTER.
- YOU'RE A STRONG PERSON, WILL.
NOT ME, I CAN'T
MAKE MYSELF LAUGH.
- BECAUSE YOU
CAN'T FEEL ANYTHING,
YOU'RE JUST A MACHINE!
- I STILL DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO LAUGH ABOUT.
- Will: I'M TELLING YOU.
THROW IT ALL AWAY.
WHETHER IT'S FAMILY,
OR FRIENDS,
LOVE, LIFE, WHATEVER IT IS,
YOU CAN THROW IT ALL AWAY AND
START OVER ANYTIME YOU WANT.
ALL IT TAKES IS THE DECISION TO
DO IT, AND IT'S ALL GONE, BUT...
I REMEMBER THE REST.
BUT IF I'M WORRIED
ABOUT REGRETS,
I SHOULD TRY TO HOLD
ON TO EVERYTHING
A LITTLE BIT LONGER, RIGHT?
THEN I CAN ALWAYS
THROW IT AWAY LATER.
SIMPLE AS THAT.
YOU MAKE IT SOUND EASY.
YOU'RE GOOD AT THAT.
- ( chuckles ) YEAH WELL...
- DO YOU THINK I'LL BE ABLE TO
LAUGH AGAIN SOME DAY?
I MEAN, AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED, CAN I?
- ( sobbing loudly )
- ( door opening )
- SO THEN, DID YOU ENJOY
YOUR MAIDEN FLIGHT?
- YES.
- CONGRATULATIONS. I'M SURE
WILL WOULD BE HAPPY FOR YOU.
- WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
IF I ASKED YOU A QUESTION?
- GO AHEAD.
- IT'S ABOUT SOMETHING WILL
SAID TO ME, THERE AT THE END.
HE SAID,
HE JUST WANTED TO LEAVE HIS
OWN LITTLE MARK ON THE WORLD,
WHILE THERE WAS STILL TIME.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
HE MEANT BY THAT?
- I THINK HE JUST WANTED
SOMEONE TO REMEMBER HIM.
HE WANTED TO KNOW THAT,
AFTER HE WAS GONE,
THERE WOULD BE AT LEAST
ONE PERSON IN THIS WORLD
TO KEEP HIS MEMORY ALIVE.
PERHAPS IT WAS SELFISH,
PLACING THAT
RESPONSIBILITY ON YOU.
- NO. I'LL NEVER FORGET WILL.
I'LL CARRY HIS MEMORY
WITH ME, ALWAYS.
- WELL, GOOD.
- ALL OF MY MEMORIES OF WILL,
OF EVERYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED,
I'LL NEVER THROW
ANY OF THEM AWAY.
THEY'RE ALL I HAVE.
- AS FOR YOUR FUTURE PLANS,
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW ABOUT THEM.
ALL I WILL SAY IS SAFE TRAVELS
AND GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR ALL YOU'VE DONE.
- ( door closes )
- TIMES CHANGE, FOR BETTER,
OR FOR WORSE, AND YET I REMAIN,
CLINGING HOPELESSLY TO A
PAST I CAN NEVER CHANGE.
AN OLD MAN AND HIS OBSESSION.
- WHERE'S THE DIRECTOR?
HE'S USUALLY NOT LATE.
- HE PROBABLY GOT
TIED UP SOMEWHERE.
THOUGH IT IS A BIT ODD
THAT HE CALLED A MEETING
SO LATE IN THE DAY.
SO, WHAT'S IT ABOUT?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA?
- NONE. I'M AS CLUELESS
AS YOU ARE.
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU
BUT I'LL HANG AROUND HERE
ALL NIGHT IF I HAVE TO.
BECAUSE THE MORE WE WAIT,
THE MORE OVERTIME WE GET.
- Silvia: OH SHUT UP, CELICA.
- WHY SHOULD I?
YOU KNOW I'M RIGHT.
- GOOD EVENING.
PLEASE EXCUSE MY TARDINESS.
I WAS STUCK IN A MEETING
THAT RAN LONG.
- AN APOLOGY ISN'T
NECESSARY, SIR.
- NOW THEN, AS FOR THE BUSINESS
AT HAND I WILL TRY TO BE BRIEF.
YOU ALL KNOW THAT I
HAVE SPECIFIC STANDARDS
I LOOK FOR WHEN CHOOSING
MY SUBORDINATES,
WHICH MUST ALL BE MET
BEFORE INITIAL CONSIDERATION.
- LIKE THEY HAVE TO BE PRETTY?
- BE QUIET.
- MORE ACCURATELY, THEY HAVE
TO BE SUPERIOR INDIVIDUALS.
GENDER, AGE, EDUCATION,
IMPORTANT, BUT NONE OF THESE
FACTORS HAVE ANY BEARING
ON THE SELECTION PROCESS.
THE FOUR OF YOU ARE YOURSELVES
SUPERIOR INDIVIDUALS,
WHICH IS WHY I PERSONALLY
SELECTED YOU TO WORK FOR ME.
IT FOLLOWS THEN, THAT
SHOULD AN INDIVIDUAL APPEAR
WHOSE ABILITIES
EXCEED YOUR OWN,
THAT INDIVIDUAL SHOULD
BE PLACED IN A POSITION
OF HIGHER AUTHORITY.
SO, THAT BEING SAID...
- ( all gasping )
- I'M PLEASED TO INTRODUCE
YOU TO YOUR NEW SUPERIOR
AS OF TODAY, ROSE ANDERSON.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Rose: I WILL NEVER SEE
YOU AS MY FATHER.
- Axela: SILVIA!
- Solty: NEXT TIME, "LADY."
YOUNG WOMEN BLOSSOM
WHEN THEY FALL IN LOVE.