- Solty: NOW LET'S SEE.
THE BALLOONS WOULD
LOOK GOOD OVER THERE.
AND WHAT ELSE WILL WE NEED?
( giggles )
- HEY, WHAT'S UP WITH HER?
- HMM? DUNNO.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
ASK HER YOURSELF?
( yawns )
- Roy: SOLTY.
- YEAH? WHAT DO YOU NEED?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY'RE YOU SO...
I DON'T KNOW. I MEAN...
AW, HELL.
- HE WANTS TO KNOW WHY
YOU'RE SO DAMN CHIPPER.
- UH, YEAH.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
- WELL, IT'S BECAUSE...
- BECAUSE OF WHAT?
- ( giggles )
IT'S A SECRET!
- I SHOULDN'T HAVE ASKED.
- OH! I REMEMBER NOW!
IT'S BECAUSE IT'S ALMOST YOUR...
- ( Solty laughs nervously )
OH, GOSH, LOOK AT THE TIME!
WE'VE GOT TO GET GOING!
- Rose: HEY!
- WELL, WE'LL SEE YOU LATER!
( laughs nervously )
- SOLTY, WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- WHAT THE...
WHY? WHY GIRLS?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ROSE, YOU'VE GOT TO
TRY TO BE MORE CAREFUL.
PLEASE WILL YOU?
- YEAH, OKAY. IT WAS MY BAD,
BUT HEY, NO HARM DONE, RIGHT?
- COME ON,
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE A SECRET!
WE CAN'T LET HIM FIND
OUT WHAT WE'RE UP TO!
IT WOULD MESS UP
THE SURPRISE PARTY!
- I'M FAMILIAR WITH THE CONCEPT.
BESIDES, YOU NEARLY
GAVE THE WHOLE THING AWAY
WITH YOUR LITTLE
MISS SUNSHINE ROUTINE.
AND ANYWAY,
NOBODY DOES BIRTHDAY PARTIES
ANYMORE, IT'S OLD FASHIONED.
- Miranda: WHO SAYS?
WE HAVE A BIRTHDAY
PARTY HERE EVERY YEAR.
RIGHT, KASHA?
- MM-HMM.
- WELL, SURE, THAT'S
FINE KIDS AND ALL,
BUT LET'S BE REALISTIC,
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
AN OLD GUY HERE,
HE'S STARING
RETIREMENT IN THE FACE.
- WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW OLD YOU ARE.
WHAT COUNTS IS HOW
YOUNG YOU ARE AT HEART!
- GEEZ LOUEEZ.
DON'T YOU SOUND PROFOUND.
ACTUALLY, THAT'S
WHAT MIRANDA SAID.
- I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
- I'LL BET ROY THINKS
WE FORGOT HIS BIRTHDAY.
WE'LL WORK ALL DAY AND
ALL NIGHT IF WE HAVE TO,
AND THROW HIM THE
BEST PARTY EVER!
HE'LL BE SO SURPRISED HE
WON'T BE ABLE TO STOP SMILING!
- WELL, WHOOP-DE-DOO.
- I CAN HARDLY WAIT
TO SEE HIS FACE.
- THIS IS GOING TO
BE SO MUCH FUN!
- YEAH!
- ARE YOU IN ON THIS ONE TOO?
- HEY, I'M JUST A KID. I GOTTA
DO WHAT THE ADULTS TELL ME TO.
- ( Rose grunts )
- OH, COME ON, ROSE.
YOU'LL HELP US, WON'T YOU?
PLEASE SAY YOU WILL!
- YEAH, SURE. WHATEVER.
- ( giggles )
- Solty: MIRANDA,
I NEED TO KNOW ABOUT THE
FOOD SO I CAN START SHOPPING.
- Miranda: DON'T WORRY.
I'VE GOT IT ALL WRITTEN DOWN.
- Solty: WHAT ABOUT
THE DECORATIONS?
- Miranda: KASHA AND I
WILL TAKE CARE OF THAT.
- Miranda: DON'T WORRY ABOUT
A THING, IT'S ALL COVERED.
- Kasha: DON'T STRAIN YOURSELF.
- NASTY!
- I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
- IS ALL THIS BLOOD?
- Axela: THE VICTIM'S NAME
IS EREL BEANE.
ENGINEER FOR R.U.C. RESEMBLE
RESEARCH, NO CRIMINAL RECORD,
HIS FAMILY FILED A MISSING
PERSONS REPORT A FEW DAYS AGO.
- AH, SO HE WAS AN R.U.C. MAN,
WAS HE?
HMM, WELL, THERE YOU ARE.
GUESS THAT EXPLAINS WHY
THEY CALLED US IN ON THIS.
- THAT'S WHAT I WAS THINKING.
- JESUS, HOW CAN THERE BE SO
MUCH BLOOD BUT NO CORPSE?
- THERE WAS A CORPSE,
MORE OR LESS.
ACCORDING TO CSI, SOMEBODY PUT
A BOMB INSIDE THE GUY'S BODY
AND THEN DETONATED IT.
WHEN THEY FIRST GOT HERE, THE
POLICE FOUND THE VICTIM'S SCALP,
BOTH OF HIS ARMS, BOTH LEGS
FROM THE THIGH DOWN, AND UH...
THAT'S ABOUT IT.
THE PIECES HAVE ALREADY
BEEN SENT TO THE MORGUE.
- OH, GOD.
- HAVE THEY GOT AN
ESTIMATED TIME OF DEATH?
- BASED ON THE DEGREE OF RIGOR
IN THE PARTS THAT WERE LEFT,
DEATH MUST HAVE OCCURRED
BETWEEN 28 AND 36 HOURS AGO.
- OH, GOD.
- SO WE'VE GOT AN ISOLATED
ABANDONED BUILDING.
SOMEBODY ABDUCTS
A RESEMBLE ENGINEER
AND MURDERS HIM IN A ROOM
FULL OF SURGICAL EQUIPMENT.
THIS GUY WAS AFTER ONE THING.
- A RESEMBLE OPERATION.
- Integra: RIGHT, BUT THEN HE
GOES OUT OF HIS WAY TO MURDER
THE VICTIM WITH A BOMB.
NOT EXACTLY YOUR TYPICAL M.O.
SHOULD BE ENOUGH TO START
NARROWING A LIST OF SUSPECTS.
- HEY, UH, I DON'T FEEL SO GOOD.
SERIOUSLY, WE
GOTTA GO RIGHT NOW.
- Crime Scene Tech: WHAT'S THIS?
SHIT. OH, SHIT!
- ( whirring )
- EVERYONE, RUN! GET OUT!
- ( exhales )
- Larry: HERE YOU GO.
I DID THE BEST THAT I COULD.
IT'S A LIST OF WOMEN
FROM THE LOWER LEVELS
WHO MATCH THE
CONDITIONS YOU SPECIFIED.
EVEN SO, IT'S FAR FROM COMPLETE.
YOU REALLY THINK YOUR DAUGHTER
COULD BE ONE OF THEM?
- Roy: WHO KNOWS?
- YOU OWE ME BIG FOR THIS.
- YOUR SISTER STILL
LIVES AT MY PLACE.
I FIGURE WE'RE SQUARE.
- Toy Robot: HAPPY
BIRTHDAY TO YOU.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DEAR ROY!
- LOOK OUT!
- ( Roy and Larry coughing )
- Roy: IF THAT'S YOUR IDEA
OF A BIRTHDAY PRANK,
I AM NOT A FAN OF IT.
( grunts )
- WHAT THE HELL WAS
THAT ALL ABOUT?
- ( telephone rings )
- ROY, MY OLD FRIEND.
DID YOU LIKE THE BIRTHDAY
PRESENT I SENT YOU?
- HO CHU?
- ( Ho Chu chuckles )
YOU REMEMBER ME! I'M SO GLAD!
- ( door bell dings )
- Solty: COMING!
JUST A MINUTE!
- Kasha: WE ARE JUST
BAKING A CAKE.
WHY DOES IT HAVE TO
BE SUCH A BIG SECRET?
- Miranda: WE DON'T WANT ROY TO
FIND OUT WHAT'S GOING ON, DO WE?
- CAN I HELP YOU WITH SOMETHING?
- YEAH, GOT A PACKAGE
FOR YOU HERE, LITTLE LADY.
- OH?
- THAT'S RIGHT,
SPECIAL DELIVERY.
- Ho Chu: FOR REVENGE,
OF COURSE.
OH, AND I'VE REPLACED
THE ARM YOU MUTILATED.
ISN'T THIS RESEMBLE
TECHNOLOGY AMAZING?
I HAVE TO SAY, I'M A VERY
SATISFIED CUSTOMER.
I'M ABLE TO CREATE
EVEN MORE INTRICATE
AND BEAUTIFUL BOMBS THAN BEFORE.
- WHEN DID YOU GET OUT?
- Ho Chu: ABOUT A MONTH AGO.
I, UH, LET MYSELF OUT.
- AND WHERE ARE YOU NOW?
- WHO KNOWS?
WHERE DO YOU THINK?
- ( grunts )
- Ho Chu: EASY, ROY. I'M SAVING
YOU FOR THE MAIN COURSE.
BUT BEFORE I SAVOR
THAT PARTICULAR MEAL,
I THINK I'LL START
WITH AN HORS D'OEUVRE.
- YOU WOULDN'T!
- Ho Chu: OH, YES!
- Miranda: WHO WAS
THAT AT THE DOOR?
- Solty: OH, IT WAS A PACKAGE,
FOR ROY.
- Miranda: FOR ROY?
HERE? WHO'S THE SENDER?
- Solty: LET'S SEE.
LOOKS LIKE A MISTER HO CHU.
- HO?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- GET RID OF IT! THROW IT
OUT THE WINDOW, QUICKLY!
- HUH?
- ( explosion booms )
- ( laughs )
OH, THAT IS SUCH A LOVELY
SOUND, DON'T YOU AGREE?
MY BOMBS ARE TRULY WORKS
OF SWEET CHAOTIC ART!
- BASTARD!
- ( Ho Chu laughs )
OH, I WISH I COULD SEE THE
LOOK ON YOUR FACE RIGHT NOW!
BUT I DON'T WANT TO
GET AHEAD OF MYSELF.
ALWAYS SAVE THE BEST FOR LAST,
THAT'S WHAT I SAY.
- HO!
- SO, PLEASE, TRY NOT
TO DIE TOO SOON.
- STOP THIS!
- IF YOU DON'T MIND.
- WE CAN MAKE A DEAL.
JUST TELL ME WHERE YOU
ARE. WE CAN MEET YOU.
- ( beeping tone )
- WHAT'S THAT?
AH!
- ( police sirens wailing )
- ( exhales )
- HELLO LADIES,
YOU'RE LOOKING BETTER.
I BROUGHT THESE TO
BRIGHTEN UP YOUR ROOM.
HOPE YOU LIKE THEM.
- UH, THANK YOU,
THEY'RE LOVELY, I...
- HEY, JUST, TAKE IT EASY.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE
FEELING BETTER SILVIA.
I WISH I COULD STAY BUT I HAVE
A MEETING I HAVE TO GET TO.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER, OKAY?
- YEAH, SURE,
AND THANK YOU FOR THE FLOWERS!
- IT WAS MY PLEASURE.
- HOPE WE'RE NOT
INTERRUPTING ANYTHING.
- UH...
- OH, THANKS FOR THE FLOWERS!
- WHA... DON'T BE AN IDIOT,
YOU MUST HAVE BRAIN DAMAGE!
- OKAY, THEN!
WHAT GOODIES DID YOU BRING US?
- OW, OW, OW...
- HA, HA, HA, HA.
- WHAT A RELIEF! YOU TWO ARE
DOING BETTER THAN I THOUGHT.
- NO, WE'RE NOT,
WE FEEL TERRIBLE.
DID YOU BRING US A CAKE?
A MELON?
SOME NUTS?
YOU MUST'VE BROUGHT SOMETHING!
- YEP, WE BROUGHT YOU
YOUR INSURANCE FORMS.
- THAT REALLY SUCKS.
- SO WHAT ABOUT THE CASE?
YOU STILL ON IT?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
FOR NOW, YOU TWO
JUST TAKE IT EASY
AND CONCENTRATE ON
GETTING WELL SOON, OKAY?
HERE YOU GO.
WE'LL BE BACK LATER.
- I, UH... GLAD YOU GUYS
DIDN'T GET BLOWN UP.
- NO MELON?
- Integra: WHERE ARE YOU ON
THE ANALYSIS OF THE PERP'S MO?
- Axela: ALL DONE.
- DID YOU TURN UP
ANY LIKELY SUSPECTS?
- FOUND ONLY ONE MAN THAT
COMBINES THESE METHODS
WITH THIS KIND OF SADISM.
HIS NAME IS HO CHU.
HE WAS THE MASTERMIND BEHIND
THOSE SKYSCRAPER BOMBINGS
A FEW YEARS AGO.
EXCEPT HE BROKE OUT OF
CERBERUS PRISON LAST MONTH,
AND NO ONE'S SEEN HIM SINCE.
- THEN WE'LL JUST HAVE
TO TRACK HIM DOWN.
- RIGHT!
- ( both grunt )
( panting )
- A NICE MESS YOU GOT ME INTO!
- FILE A COMPLAINT
WITH MY OFFICE.
- I SWEAR TO GOD
IF ROSE IS HURT...
- JUST ABOUT TO CALL
'EM CHECK ON THAT.
IF YOU'D GET OUT OF MY WAY.
WOULD YOU MOVE OR SOMETHING!
- I'M STUCK.
- ( phone rings )
- Roy: COME ON. DAMN IT!
THERE'S NO ANSWER!
- I WARN YOU, IF ANYTHING
HAPPENS TO ROSE...
- WOULD YOU SHUT UP!
TRY THE HUNTERS' OFFICE.
DISCONNECTED.
- ROY, I HAVE TO...
- DO IT.
- Man: WAIT, PLEASE.
YOU MUSTN'T GO. PLEASE DON'T.
HE'LL KILL ME IF YOU DO.
- KNOW THIS GUY?
- ( phone rings )
- ANSWER IT.
ANSWER THE PHONE. QUICKLY.
PLEASE!
HE'LL KILL ME.
- ( phone rings )
- Man: PICK UP THE PHONE.
- ( phone continues to ring )
- SAVE ME.
I'M BEGGING YOU!
- ( phone continues to ring )
- Ho Chu: ROY, MY FRIEND,
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE. WELL DONE!
- HO, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- AREN'T YOU ENJOYING THE GAME?
BUT YOU'RE DOING SO WELL,
YOU MADE IT PAST
THE FIRST LEVEL.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR LEVEL TWO.
- WHAT?
- DO YOU SEE THAT BOX
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE STREET,
SITTING ON THE MEDIAN?
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE ONE THAT ADORABLE LITTLE
BOY IS LOOKING AT RIGHT NOW.
THERE'S A BOMB IN THAT BOX.
WHAT'S MORE, IT'S
SYNCHRONIZED WITH
THE BOMB THAT'S STRAPPED
TO THAT MAN BEHIND YOU.
IF YOU DON'T DISARM BOTH BOMBS
AT THE EXACT SAME MOMENT...
KA BOOM.
- YOU SON OF A...
- IT'S LIKE I TOLD YOU,
IT'S A GAME.
JUST RELAX, YOU HAVE
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
I'LL TELL YOU HOW
TO DISARM THEM.
- AND IF I REFUSE TO PLAY?
- OH, LOOK, I HAVE
A REMOTE CONTROL DETONATOR.
I WONDER IF IT WORKS?
ARE WE ON THE
SAME PAGE NOW, ROY?
- BUT I CAN'T DISARM THEM
BOTH AT THE SAME TIME!
- YOU HAVE AN ASSISTANT
RIGHT NEXT YOU.
I'M SURE MR. ANDERSON WILL
BE DELIGHTED TO LEND A HAND.
- Larry: SCREW YOU.
- HEY! WHAT ARE YOU...
- THIS IS NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
- ( explosion booms )
- ( phone rings )
- Ho Chu: YOU'RE NOT
GOING ANYWHERE, LARRY.
IF YOU PULL ANOTHER
STUNT LIKE THAT,
I'LL DETONATE THE BOMB
ON THAT MAN'S CHEST.
- YOU WIN, FREAK.
I'LL PLAY ALONG WITH YOUR
GAME FOR THE TIME BEING.
- OKAY! LET THE GAME BEGIN!
ROY, YOU TAKE THE
ONE ACROSS THE STREET.
A PANEL INSIDE THE BOX WILL
TELL YOU HOW TO DISARM IT.
- ( cars honking )
- Driver: ASSHOLE!
- Little Boy: HEY, GRAMPS.
DON'T YOU KNOW YOU SHOULD
CROSS AT THE CORNER?
- ACTUALLY, THAT
PACKAGE THERE IS MINE.
GUESS I MUST HAVE DROPPED IT.
- REALLY?
- Ho Chu: OKAY, FIRST, PULL THE
PIN ATTACHED TO THE BLUE CABLE.
- HOLD STILL AND STAY CALM.
- ALL RIGHT, TO START WE
GOTTA TAKE OFF THE TOP COVER.
- I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO STAY CALM!
- THERE, NOW WHAT COMES NEXT?
- WHY IN THE HELL
AM I DOING THIS?
- WHAT'S NEXT? COME ON, WHAT'S
NEXT? HURRY UP AND TELL ME!
- DAMN IT! IS THIS THE ONE?
- ( laughs maliciously )
LARRY, BE VERY CAREFUL
WHEN YOU PULL THAT ONE OUT.
CAREFUL. CAREFUL.
( laughs maliciously )
EASY!
SEE THAT LITTLE METAL BALL?
IF THAT METAL BALL TOUCHES
EITHER END OF THAT GLASS TUBE,
IT'S PARTY TIME!
- MOTHER F... STOP MOVING!
- Ho Chu: OOO!
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE!
YOU DON'T WANT TO END UP
LIKE YOUR BROTHER, DO YOU?
- WHAT?
WHAT DID YOU DO TO ANDY,
YOU SICK MANIAC?
- I JUST SENT HIM
A LITTLE PRESENT.
I DON'T MEAN TO BE
HARSH, MY FRIEND,
BUT I REALLY THINK YOU
SHOULD BE WORRYING
ABOUT YOURSELF AT THE MOMENT.
- YOU'RE DEAD. YOU HEAR ME?
- YES, GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
- Roy: NO!
I COULDN'T READ IT!
GET OUT OF HERE, KID!
- Ho Chu: OH, WELL PLAYED!
NOW THERE'S ONLY ONE STEP LEFT.
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT'S
ABOUT ALL I CAN TELL YOU.
- SAY WHAT?
- Ho Chu: MY GAME, MY RULES.
- YOU CAN'T DO THIS!
- A PLAYER CAN'T WIN
THE GAME IF HE'S FAINT OF HEART.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE
THE PROPER SPIRIT.
YOU CAN ONLY WIN IF
YOU'RE BRAVE ENOUGH.
- YOU HAD IT PLANNED
LIKE THIS FROM THE START!
- YOUR HINT IS BRAVERY.
- ( tone beeping )
- Roy: BRAVERY?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- ( Man with bomb cries )
- Larry: LOOK, I'M SORRY, MAN.
BUT THERE'S NO TIME LEFT.
GET DOWN INTO THAT MANHOLE.
IT'LL KEEP CASUALTIES
TO A MINIMUM.
- NO. NO, PLEASE.
- GET MOVING!
- YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
PLEASE, I HAVE A FAMILY.
( cries )
DON'T! PLEASE!
- NO, LARRY, DON'T DO IT!
LARRY, DON'T SHOOT!
- ( phone beeps )
- Roy: WE'VE BEEN PLAYED.
THESE BOMBS ARE DUMMIES.
THE WHOLE THING WAS A SET UP.
- Larry: HO CHU.
YOU'RE A DEAD MAN.
WHEN I FIND YOU...
- Rose: HMM.
A BIRTHDAY PRESENT, HUH?
WHAT A PAIN.
OH, WELL, I HAVE BEEN
CRASHING THERE RENT FREE.
IT'S PROBABLY A
PRETTY GOOD IDEA FOR ME
TO TRY AND STAY ON THE
LANDLADY'S GOOD SIDE.
- Ho Chu: EXCUSE ME.
- WHO, ME?
- Roy: HEY.
- ROY!
- ARE YOU AND KASHA BOTH OKAY?
- YES, WE ARE THANK GOODNESS.
- WHAT ABOUT SOLTY?
WHERE IS SHE?
- RIGHT HERE!
AH, I'M GOOD AS NEW.
- SO, EVERYONE'S OKAY?
- IT WAS SOLTY WHO
SAVED OUR LIVES.
OTHERWISE THINGS WOULD'VE
BEEN WORSE THAN THIS.
- SHE WAS SO AWESOME!
SHE GRABBED THE BOMB AND
THREW IT OUT THE WINDOW
JUST A SECOND
BEFORE IT EXPLODED!
- GET RID OF IT!
- Kasha: IT WAS GREAT! ALL
THE SOOT FROM THE EXPLOSION
MADE HER LOOK LIKE
A CHIMNEY SWEEP!
- YEAH, THAT'S GOOD.
- ROY, IT'S...
IT'S HO CHU AGAIN.
- OH, I KNOW. MIRANDA,
I WANT YOU TO GET AS MANY
HUNTERS TOGETHER AS
YOU CAN FOR PROTECTION.
CHECK INTO A HOTEL
FOR THE NIGHT.
IT'S NOT GOOD TO STAY HERE.
I'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU LATER.
- YOU'RE GONNA GO OUT
AFTER HIM, AREN'T YOU?
WELL, I WANT A
PIECE OF HIM MYSELF.
I WHAT THAT BASTARD TO PAY
FOR WHAT HE DID TO MY OFFICE!
- I WANNA HELP TOO,
COUNT ME IN!
- I'M NOT STAYING IN
A HOTEL BY MYSELF
WITH JUST A BUNCH OF
CREEPY HUNTERS AROUND!
- ( grunts )
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I GUESS IT'LL BE
EASIER TO PROTECT YOU IF
YOU ALL IN THE SAME PLACE.
OKAY, FIRST WE
HAVE TO FIND ROSE.
THEN WE NEED ALL THE INFO
WE CAN GET ON HO.
- ( machine beeping )
- Roy: HAVE YOU FOUND OUT
WHERE ROSE IS YET?
- Miranda: I'VE GOT MEN
LOOKING FOR HER NOW.
- AND WHAT ABOUT HO?
- I CAN TRACK HIS WHEREABOUTS
UP UNTIL TWO DAYS AGO.
AFTER THAT, GONE
WITHOUT A TRACE.
- WELL, KEEP ON IT.
- I WILL.
- ( Solty humming )
( humming continues)
- Roy: SOLTY!
- ( stops humming )
- YES? WHAT IS IT?
- WHAT WAS THAT TUNE
YOU WERE HUMMING?
- OH! THAT'S JUST A LITTLE SONG
ROSE TAUGHT ME THE OTHER DAY.
SHE SAID SINGING IT HELPS HER
FEEL BETTER WHEN SHE'S TENSE.
SO I THOUGHT IF I SANG IT,
YOU'D FEEL BETTER.
HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
- YOU MEAN ROSE WAS
SINGING THAT SONG?
- ( Sarah humming )
- Miranda: WHAT'S THAT?
- Yuto: IT WAS IN THE MAILBOX,
ADDRESSED TO ROY.
I SCANNED IT FOR ALL
KNOWN EXPLOSIVES
AND IT CAME OUT CLEAN.
IT'S A VIDEO DISK.
- A VIDEO DISK, HUH?
- YEP.
- HELLO ROY, OLD FRIEND.
I HOPE YOU HAD FUN
THE OTHER DAY. I DID.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
MISS ROSE HAS JOINED THE GAME.
YOU CAN RELAX.
SHE'S STILL ALIVE, FOR NOW.
COME TO THE CROWN CENTER
BUILDING ON SOUTH 3RD STREET.
COME ALONE, OF COURSE.
IT'S TIME FOR THE FINAL LEVEL.
( laughs maliciously )
- ( closing theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Solty: ROSE...
- Roy: I SWEAR, I'LL...
- Solty: NEXT TIME,
"TEARS, AFTER THE SHOWDOWN."
( Solty screams )