- ( gun cocking )
- ( screams )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( groaning )
- DALE BOYD,
24 COUNTS OF THEFT,
11 COUNTS, ASSAULT,
6 COUNTS, SEXUAL ASSAULT.
GAME'S UP. I'M BRINGING YOU IN
FOR THE BOUNTY.
- SINCE WHEN'S THIS
THE WAY YOU HUNTERS WORK?
BOUNTY OR NO BOUNTY,
I'M NOT RESISTING HERE, MAN.
YOU CAN'T SHOOT...
UH, YOU... YOU CAN'T SHOOT ME.
THEY'LL REVOKE YOUR LICENSE.
- OH, SHUT UP.
THIS IS THE WAY I WORK.
- HOLD IT!
INTEGRA, WE'RE CLOSING IN.
- SO, WHO IS THIS
WE'RE CHASING, ANYWAY?
- LOOK SHARP OUT THERE,
YOU GUYS.
YOUR TARGET WAS CAUGHT BREAKING
INTO A TOP SECURITY AREA.
WE WANT HER BROUGHT IN
FOR QUESTIONING, IMMEDIATELY.
- ROGER THAT.
CELICA, STAY BACK.
- OKAY. JUST GO EASY
THIS TIME, SILVIA.
I THINK THE IDEA IS,
THEY WANT HER ALIVE.
- YEAH, THANKS. I KNOW.
( groans )
- THAT'S ENOUGH! WHAT IN THE
HECK ARE YOU, SOME KIND OF...
- SORRY, SHE, UH, SHE GOT AWAY.
- WHAT DO YOU HAVE, AXELA?
- NOTHING. WE'RE PICKING UP WAY
TOO MUCH AURORA INTERFERENCE.
IT'S JAMMING UP
ALL OF OUR SENSORS.
WE'VE LOST THE TARGET.
- BASTARD! MY PARTNER'LL HAVE
SOMETHING TO SAY ABOUT THIS!
- YOU SCUMBAGS ARE ALL THE SAME.
LEMME GUESS, THIS IS THE PART
WHERE YOU START MAKING THREATS?
- OKAY, JUST TAKE IT EASY, MAN.
YOU GOT ME.
I... I GIVE UP, ALL RIGHT?
GO AHEAD, TAKE ME IN.
( laughs )
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
WHERE THE HELL DID HE GO?
- NICE TRY, ASSHOLE.
YOU PUNKS GO OUT
AND GET A RESEMBLE ARM,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN, YOU
START THINKING YOU'RE CLEVER.
- DON'T SHOOT!
COME ON, CUT ME A BREAK.
I'M JUST A SMALL-TIMER.
I ONLY STEAL TO GET BY SINCE I
LOST MY ARM IN THE BLAST FALL.
WHATEVER THE BOUNTY ON ME IS,
IT CAN'T BE WORTH
KILLING ME OVER!
- YOU WERE IN THE BLAST FALL?
- TELL YOU WHAT,
LET'S MAKE A DEAL.
WHATEVER THEY'RE PAYING YOU,
I'LL DOUBLE IT, YEAH?
COME ON, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- WHY ARE YOU STILL BREATHING?
WHY IS A WORTHLESS PIECE OF SHIT
LIKE YOU STILL ALIVE?
- HEY, WAIT! ( groaning )
WAIT! NO! STOP IT!
- Newscaster on TV:
AND NOW,
HERE ARE HIS MORNING'S
TOP HEADLINES.
YESTERDAY, A PANEL OF
LEADING EXPERTS TESTIFIED
BEFORE AN R.U.C.
GOVERNMENT SECTOR SUBCOMMITTEE
IN REGARD TO
THE ALTITUDE CEILING.
ACCORDING TO THEIR FINDINGS,
AURORA WAVE ELECTROMAGNETIC
PRESSURE LEVELS HAVE REMAINED
VIRTUALLY UNCHANGED OVER
THE LAST 12-MONTH PERIOD.
BASED ON THIS EVIDENCE,
THE COMMITTEE AGREED UNANIMOUSLY
TO ONCE AGAIN
POSTPONE REVISION
OF THE ALTITUDE CEILING
UNTIL NEXT YEAR.
TODAY'S WEATHER FORECAST.
CLEAR SKIES AND A LIGHT
SOUTHERLY BREEZE SHOULD MAKE
FOR PLEASANT CONDITIONS
THROUGHOUT THE AFTERNOON.
HOWEVER, SOME AREAS
WILL BE STRONGLY AFFECTED
BY THE AURORA...
- ( door opens and closes )
- R.U.C. IS PROUD
TO BRING YOU
THE LATEST IN RESEMBLE ARMS.
SUCH AS, THE RZ88. FEATURING
STATE OF THE ART DESIGN,
PROVING THAT HIGH PERFORMANCE
DOESN'T HAVE TO COME
AT A HIGH PRICE!
IT'S THE NAME YOU TRUST FOR
ALL YOUR RESEMBLE NEEDS, R.U.C.!
R.U.C. IS PROUD TO
BRING YOU THE LATEST...
- HELLO. AND WELCOME
TO MAVERICK HUNTERS AGENCY!
WE'RE HERE WHEN YOU NEED US,
ANY TIME DAY OR NIGHT.
OR MY NAME ISN'T
MIRANDA MAVERICK!
WHETHER IT'S SEARCHING
FOR YOUR LOST CAT,
OR TRACKING DOWN A CAT BURGLAR,
WHEN SOMETHING NEEDS FINDING,
COUNT ON OUR TEAM OF
PROFESSIONAL HUNTERS
TO FIND IT, GUARANTEED!
NO JOB IS TOO BIG OR TOO SMALL.
( sighs ) DO I HAVE TO SAY THAT,
KASHA? REALLY?
- YES, YOU DO!
I MEAN, WE'RE AN
UP-AND-COMING BUSINESS,
AND THE TV NEWS PEOPLE
WANNA DO A STORY ON YOU.
WE GOTTA JUMP ON
THE FREE ADVERTISING.
- YES, BUT, KASHA...
- IT'S CALLED "ACTING", MOM.
TRUST ME, YOU JUST GOTTA
GO WITH IT, OKAY?
NOW ONCE MORE!
WITH FEELING THIS TIME!
GOT IT?
- ( groans )
- SAY, UH...
YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT US
TO DO ANYTHING?
- QUIET ON THE SET!
READY! ACTION!
- AND HELLO! WELCOME TO
MAVERICK HUNTERS AGENCY!
WE'RE HERE ANY TIME
YOU NEED US, DAY OR...
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- OH, UH, ROY...
- JUST NEED TO CERTIFY
COMPLETION OF THE DALE BOYD JOB
AND PICK UP AN AMMO REFILL.
THEN I'LL BE OUTTA YOUR HAIR.
- OKAY. SURE.
- DALE BOYD, HUH?
I HEAR HE WAS IN PRETTY ROUGH
SHAPE WHEN YOU BROUGHT
HIM IN YESTERDAY.
- EH, HE'LL LIVE.
- ( grunts ) YOU! SO WHAT?
THAT'S NOT THE POINT!
WE'VE GOT A REPUTATION
TO THINK ABOUT!
IF ONE OF OUR HUNTERS IS
OUT THERE ACTING LIKE A MANIAC,
IT MAKES THE WHOLE OFFICE
LOOK BAD! WRONG WITH YOU?
- THAT S.O.B.'S
AS CRAZY AS EVER.
- YEAH. POOR BASTARD NEVER
GOT OVER HIS DAUGHTER'S DEATH!
WHAT'S IT BEEN, 12 YEARS?
- COOL IT, MISTER!
YOU GOT ME?
- ROY, COULD YOU LINK UP FOR ME?
- YEAH.
- OKAY. THAT CERTIFIES
THE CAPTURE OF DALE BOYD.
I'LL GO AHEAD AND WIRE
THE BOUNTY TO YOUR ACCOUNT.
AND, ONE MORE TIME
FOR THE AMMO REFILL.
- GREAT. NOW LISTEN.
PLEASE BE MORE CAREFUL.
IF ANYTHING HAPPENED
TO YOU OUT THERE,
SARAH WOULD NEVER FORGIVE ME.
OH, AND, ROY...
IT'S BEEN A COUPLE OF WEEKS,
I STILL HAVEN'T GOTTEN
THIS MONTH'S RENT.
- YEAH, WELL TAKE IT OUT OF
MY PAY LIKE YOU ALWAYS DO.
- OH, COME ON,
THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
I DON'T CARE IF HE WAS
YOUR BEST FRIEND'S HUSBAND!
YOU GOTTA STOP BEING
SO EASY ON HIM!
- I KNOW.
BUT WHAT ELSE CAN I DO?
- ( sighs )
- Roy: SO, UH, HOW DO YOU
LIKE YOUR NEW SHOES?
- I LOVE 'EM, DADDY!
THEY'RE SO PRETTY!
- GOOD. ( chuckles )
( sobs )
- Man onTV: THOUGH THE EXACT
CAUSES ARE STILL UNCLEAR,
THE INVESTIGATION
INTO THE RECENT ACCIDENT
HAS REVEALED AN ABNORMAL RISE
IN AURORA WAVE ELECTROMAGNETIC
PRESSURE LEVELS.
AT PRESENT,
THE DEATH COUNT STANDS...
- ( grunts )
( sobs ) NO. SHE'S NOT DEAD.
MY RITA'S NOT DEAD!
I SWEAR, I WILL FIND HER,
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES!
- ( laughs ) OKAY.
BUT WHAT SHOULD WE EAT
FOR DINNER TONIGHT?
- UM, PASGHETTI!
- REALLY?
- MM-HMM!
- ( laughs ) ALL RIGHT.
"PASGHETTI" IT IS.
- ( in sing-song voice )
PASGHETTI, PASGHETTI!
- ( explosion )
- ( groans )
- MY PARTNER DALE SAYS HELLO.
NOW DIE!
COME ON, MAN, GIVE IT UP.
I KNOW YOU'RE HERE.
HOW MUCH FURTHER YOU
THINK YOU'RE GONNA GET
ON THAT LEG, HUH?
MIGHT AS WELL COME ON OUT
AND GET IT OVER WITH.
MAKE IT EASY
ON THE BOTH OF US.
HA! HUNTER SCUM!
- YOU'RE EVEN MORE PREDICTABLE
THAN THAT STUPID-ASS
PARTNER OF YOURS.
AND FOR YOUR SAKE,
YOU BETTER HOPE YOUR BOUNTY'S
ENOUGH TO BUY ME A NEW COAT.
- HOW'S THIS FOR PREDICTABLE?
THAT'S RIGHT, I'VE STILL GOT
A FEW TRICKS UP MY SLEEVE!
AND DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE COAT.
YOU WON'T NEED IT
WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
I HEAR IT'S PRETTY WARM IN HELL!
WHA...
( groans )
- SHE SAVED MY LIFE.
BUT WHAT THE HELL IS SHE?
- ( sighs )
- SO YOU'RE AWAKE, HUH?
YOU OKAY?
- ( sobs )
- HEY! WHAT'S THE MATTER?
SO WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU IN SOME KIND OF TROUBLE,
THAT IT?
DON'T WORRY, I WON'T
CALL THE COPS ON YOU.
LEAST I CAN DO, YOU KNOW,
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
WHAT THE HELL
WERE YOU DOING OUT THERE?
AND DRESSED LIKE THAT?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
OKAY, WHERE'RE YOU FROM?
WHAT, CAN'T YOU TALK?
- NO.
NO, I MEAN, I, I CAN TALK.
- ( sighs )
I HAVE WORK TO DO.
YOU CAN KEEP THE CLOTHES.
FINISH YOUR DRINK
AND GO ON HOME.
DOOR LOCKS AUTOMATICALLY.
DON'T LET IT HIT YOU
ON THE WAY OUT.
- Man: DALE BOYD'S PARTNER.
YEAH, I KNOW HIM.
GRAY WALKER. SMALLTIME CROOK,
TWO RESEMBLE ARMS.
VINDICTIVE S.O.B., THOUGH.
I GUARANTEE
HE'LL COME AFTER YOU AGAIN.
- ANY IDEA WHERE HE'S STAYING?
- NAH. NO ONE PLACE.
LIKES TO KEEP MOVING.
YOU KNOW THE TYPE.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU AGAIN? WHAT THE HELL?
- WHAT? YOU KNOW THAT ONE
OR SOMETHING?
- ( screams )
- NO.
WOULD YOU STOP FOLLOWING ME!
- AND HERE WE ARE!
THIS IS THE BLAST FALL MEMORIAL,
BUILT IN COMMEMORATION OF ALL
THOSE WHO LOST THEIR LIVES
IN THE GREAT DISASTER
12 YEARS AGO.
- YOU GONNA TELL ME
WHY YOU'RE FOLLOWING ME?
- Guide: NOW IS THERE
ANYONE IN OUR GROUP
WHO ISN'T ALREADY
FAMILIAR WITH...
- YOU GOT A HOME
TO GO TO, RIGHT?
SO GO. WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
( sighs ) I'M LEAVING.
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
TAGGING ALONG, GOT ME?
DON'T!
- COME ON, MAN,
NO SLEEPING ON THE JOB!
( laughs ) HEY, BUDDY.
SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
- HEY.
WHY'RE YOU STILL FOLLOWING ME?
FOR THE LAST TIME,
JUST GO ON HOME.
DON'T YOU HAVE A FAMILY?
SOMETHING?
- I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
- YEAH, THAT'S SAD.
BUT I CAN'T HELP ANYMORE, KID.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE YESTERDAY,
SO I LET YOU STAY THE NIGHT.
THAT'S ALL.
GO FIND SOMEONE ELSE.
- W-WAIT.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
DO YOU HAVE A FAMILY?
- WHY DO YOU CARE?
IT'S NONE OF YOUR
DAMN BUSINESS.
NOW GO ON, GET LOST.
- HEY, ROY REVANT!
REMEMBER ME? HA!
- UH, THANK YOU,
BUT YOU REALLY...
- STUPID KID.
GET OUTTA HERE! NOW!
( groans )
- ( laughs diabolically )
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF
MY NEW TOY? NICE, HUH?
I STOLE IT FROM R.U.C. SECURITY!
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY, ROY?
LET'S HAVE SOME FUN!
YEAH! THAT'S THE WAY!
GO AHEAD AND RUN!
( laughs ) TELL YOU WHAT, WE'LL
EVEN GIVE YOU A HEAD START.
THAT LITTLE SCRATCH I GAVE HIM
IS SLOWING HIM DOWN.
- HA! SO HOW ABOUT WE PUT HIM
OUT OF HIS MISERY?
DIE, ASSHOLE!
- WHAT ARE YOU STILL DOING HERE?
- YOU DIDN'T LET ME THANK YOU
FOR SAVING ME BACK THERE.
YOU KNEW YOUR LEG WAS HURT,
BUT YOU STILL PROTECTED ME.
SO IT'S MY TURN AND NOW
I'M GOING TO PROTECT YOU.
- WHAT?
- Dale: YO, KID! WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
YOU LEAVE HIM ALONE!
- ALL RIGHT,
YOU CAN DIE WITH HIM!
SHIT! BOUNCED RIGHT OFF HER!
SHE'S A RES. SHE'S GOTTA BE!
- NO. NO WAY!
THEY DON'T MAKE RESEMBLE ARMOR
THAT STRONG!
- DAMMIT!
WHAT THE...
- HOW?
- ( Solty yells )
LIKE I TRIED TO TELL YOU,
I DON'T KNOW,
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
NOT EVEN WHO I AM.
- YOU MESSED WITH
THE WRONG GUY, KID!
- OR WHY...
- DIE!
- ...I CAN DO THINGS LIKE THIS!
I HATE BAD PEOPLE!
- THE AURORA SHELL!
WE'RE GOING TOO HIGH!
PULL OUT OF IT.
PULL OUT...
- THEY HIT THE ALTITUDE CEILING.
JESUS H. CHRIST.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE AGAIN.
YOU ASKED ME EARLIER
IF I HAD A FAMILY.
WELL, I HAD A WIFE ONCE.
BUT SHE'S DEAD NOW.
CANCER.
TIME WE CAUGHT IT,
IT WAS TOO LATE.
WE HAD A DAUGHTER,
THOUGH, RITA.
SHE'S ALL THE FAMILY
I'VE GOT LEFT.
MEANS I DON'T HAVE TIME TO DEAL
WITH YOU. DON'T FOLLOW ME.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Solty: WHERE DID
I COME FROM? WHERE?
NEXT TIME, "A NEW DAWN."
WOULD YOU MIND IF WE MET?