- Rose: A BAND OF THIEVES.
INGENIOUS, COURAGEOUS,
COVERT, BOLD...
THE FEARLESS EQUALIZERS
OF SOCIAL INJUSTICE.
KNOWN ONLY AS "TEAM ROSE"!
- Andy: WAIT A MINUTE!
WHAT'S THIS "TEAM ROSE" CRAP?
JUST TO BE CLEAR,
DESPITE WHAT YOU MAY
HAVE HEARD ON THE STREETS,
WE'RE NOT DOING ALL
THIS FOR THE MONEY.
- Andy: WHAT? YOU LIAR!
- MOST OF WHAT WE
STEAL IS GIVEN TO THE
POOR UNREGISTERED CITIZENS
WHO LACK WELFARE PROTECTION.
- WELL, YEAH. THAT'S TRUE.
- MODERN DAY ROBIN HOODS,
YOU SAY?
OH, COME ON!
THAT'S NOT WHO WE ARE AT ALL!
WE ONLY WANT TO
HELP THE NEEDY,
TO BEAR THE FLAG IN A REVOLT
AGAINST A SOCIETY WE DISDAIN.
AND IF WE GARNER A LITTLE
ATTENTION ALONG THE WAY,
IT ONLY MAKES PEOPLE MORE
AWARE OF THE PROBLEMS
THAT WE'RE OUT TO MAKE RIGHT.
THAT IS THE HEART AND MODUS
OPERANDI OF "TEAM ROSE"!
- Andy: LOOK! FOR THE LAST TIME,
WE ARE NOT "TEAM ROSE"!
- ACTUALLY, THE NAME
OF OUR LITTLE BAND IS
"THE FRIENDLY
ANDERSON BROTHERS."
- Rose: WHAT?
- Andy: WHA... OH, COME ON!
- Rose: WE'RE KIND OF
TEMPORARILY CLOSED FOR NOW.
- GOOD MORNING!
THANK YOU FOR TUNING IN.
I'M LYDIA MACKAY.
NOW FOR NEWS.
ROADS FROM
THE DOWNTOWN AREA...
- Rose: IT SAYS HERE THAT
ALL PRODUCTION HAS CEASED
ON THE ENHANCED LINEAR WHEEL.
I DIDN'T SEE THAT ONE COMING.
POST-WAR TIMES ARE
PRETTY DIFFICULT
FOR THE MANUFACTURING
SECTOR, HUH?
AND ON TOP OF THAT, MY
HOROSCOPE IS TOTALLY BORING.
SOLTY! WHEN'S YOUR BIRTHDAY?
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA, DO YOU?
THAT'S YOUR TOP STORY?
- HEY! WOULD YOU PLEASE
REMIND ME AGAIN
WHY YOU'RE STILL HERE?
- TO RECRUIT SOLTY
AS A THIEF, OF COURSE!
I THOUGHT WE
TALKED ABOUT THIS.
- LOOKS TO ME LIKE
YOU'RE SITTING AROUND
MOOCHING A FREE BREAKFAST!
SOLTY'S A SPECIAL GIRL!
SHE'S ALREADY SHOWN
TREMENDOUS POTENTIAL.
AND THAT POTENTIAL COULD BE
USED TO BENEFIT OUR SOCIETY,
BY MAKING HER
A TOP-CLASS THIEF!
- LIKE HELL YOU WILL.
- I'M NOT SURE IF I
WANNA BE A THIEF.
- WELL, YOU GOT PLENTY
OF TIME TO CONSIDER IT.
I'M GONNA BE HERE
FOR A WHILE.
- WHAT? SAYS WHO?
- IT'S REALLY THE BEST THING
FOR EVERYBODY!
IT'D BE SUCH A HASSLE TO HAVE
TO MOVE ALL MY STUFF BACK OUT.
- NOW, YOU LISTEN TO ME!
- SOMETHING ON YOUR MIND?
- SHOULDN'T WE... ALL TRY TO
GET ALONG WITH EACH OTHER?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Andy: WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- OF COURSE I'M SERIOUS,
MY DEAR BROTHER.
I'M GOING TO MAKE SOLTY A THIEF.
I MEAN JUST THINK ABOUT
ALL THE POSSIBILITIES!
IF SHE JOINS US, OUR WORK
BECOMES A WHOLE LOT EASIER.
- YOU'RE OUTTA YOUR MIND.
- I'LL BET THAT LARRY
AGREES WITH ME.
LARRY DO YOU AGREE WITH ME?
- IT'S NOT A BAD IDEA.
- Andy: YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
- Rose: I KNEW YOU'D THINK SO!
- SOLTY REVANT'S
PHYSICAL CAPABILITIES
ARE VERY IMPRESSIVE.
IT WOULD DEFINITELY BE AN ASSET
IF SHE WERE TO BECOME OUR ALLY.
HOWEVER, WE HAVE TO TAKE ROY
INTO CONSIDERATION, AS WELL.
I DON'T THINK HE'LL BE
SO WILLING TO AGREE.
- THEN I'LL JUST
HAVE TO CONVINCE HIM.
- THINK YOU CAN?
- WELL, OF COURSE!
- AND HOW SOON COULD THAT BE?
WE DON'T KNOW WHEN HE
MIGHT DECIDE TO TURN ON US.
WE CAN'T LEAVE YOU THERE
WITH HIM FOR VERY LONG.
- Rose: SO, WHAT?
- YOU GOT THREE DAYS.
THREE DAYS TO MAKE IT HAPPEN.
- LARRY!
- IF YOU CAN'T DO IT BY THEN,
GIVE UP AND BACK OFF.
THOSE ARE MY CONDITIONS
ON THE MATTER.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
AND ACCEPT THEM?
- THREE DAYS
IS MORE THAN ENOUGH TIME.
FOR ROSE, THERE'S NOTHING
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
- ( door creaks )
- ( gasps )
( breathing heavily )
WHAT DO YOU WANT!
- YOU WERE TOSSING AND TURNING
IN YOUR SLEEP.
I WAS WORRIED.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- IT'S NOTHING.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, SOLTY.
SO WHERE'D THE OLD MAN GO?
- HE SAID HE HAD SOME WORK
TO DO AND THEN HE LEFT.
- YEAH? REALLY?
- UH-HUH.
- THEN HOW ABOUT WE...
- I WON'T DO IT!
I'M NOT GONNA BE A THIEF!
- DAMN.
- Miranda: SO I HEAR THAT ROSE
IS TRYING PRETTY HARD
TO RECRUIT SOLTY
INTO A LIFE OF THIEVERY.
- AND HOW DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT ALL THAT?
- SHE TOLD ME. SHE MENTIONED
SOMETHING ABOUT IT
YESTERDAY WHEN WE WERE
AT THE TEA ROOM TOGETHER.
- WHEN DID SHE HAVE TIME TO...
- SO I'M ASSUMING THAT YOU'RE
NOT GOING LET THAT PLAN
COME TO FRUITION?
- NO! OF COURSE NOT!
- YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
I REALLY DON'T THINK THAT
ROSE IS AS BAD OF A PERSON
AS YOU MAKE HER OUT TO BE.
I MEAN SHE MAY BE A THIEF
AND ALL, BUT SHE DOES IT
SO SHE CAN HELP
ALL THOSE UNREGISTERED CITIZENS.
- DOESN'T MATTER.
A CRIMINAL IS STILL A CRIMINAL.
- WHY DO KEEP SAYING
SUCH MEAN THINGS ABOUT HER?
EVERYTHING SHE DOES
IS TO HELP PEOPLE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
JUST KEEP CALLING HER
A CRIMINAL LIKE THAT!
I THINK IT'D BE GREAT
IF SOLTY BECAME A THIEF!
THAT WAY, SHE COULD
HELP PEOPLE TOO!
I THINK SOLTY FEELS THE SAME,
BUT SHE'S TOO SCARED TO...
- ( gasps )
- Miranda: KASHA?
WHAT IS THIS?
- UM, THAT'S, UH... YOU SEE...
- UH... AND WHERE DID YOU
GET THAT RING?
- I'M SORRY.
GUESS I SCREWED UP.
- ( shushing )
- Rose: COME ON!
THINK ABOUT IT.
A PROPOSAL LIKE THIS
DOESN'T COME ALONG EVERY DAY.
THREE MEALS A DAY,
AN AFTERNOON BREAK,
AND A GUARANTEED MINIMUM WAGE!
PLUS, WITH OUR PROFIT SHARING,
THE MORE YOU WORK,
THE MORE YOU EARN.
TWO BONUSES A YEAR!
HOUSING INCLUDED!
IT'S SUCH AN EXCITING OFFER!
TAKE A LOOK AROUND!
YOU WON'T FIND
A BETTER OPPORTUNITY.
- THAT'S WHY YOU SHOULD RECON--
- ( door slams )
- HEY! WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?
WERE YOU EVEN LISTENING TO ME?
- OH! ROSE!
- UGH. WHAT'S THAT
OLD MAN'S PROBLEM?
- UH, WELL, HE...
- GUESS I'LL BE ROOMING
IN HERE AGAIN.
WELL, GREAT!
THERE'S ONLY TWO DAYS LEFT.
IF I'D KNOWN IT WAS
GONNA BE THIS HARD,
I WOULD'VE ASKED FOR THREE
MONTHS INSTEAD OF THREE DAYS.
- OKAY, ROSE.
THE BED'S ALL READY FOR YOU.
- SO, SOLTY...
- I CAN'T ROSE.
- AND HERE WE ARE!
THIS IS THE BLAST
FALL MEMORIAL,
BUILT IN COMMEMORATION
OF ALL THOSE THEIR LIVES
N THE GREAT DISASTER
12 YEARS AGO.
EVERYONE HERE IS FAMILIAR WITH
THE EVENTS OF THE
BLAST FALL, RIGHT?
- I GUESS IT WAS A CRAZY
IDEA TO BEGIN WITH.
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO
CONVINCE THE OLD MAN!
WHY IS HE SO PROTECTIVE OF HER?
IT'S NOT LIKE HE CAN
HIDE HER AWAY FOREVER.
AND I'M SURE SOLTY
WOULD BE BETTER OFF
IF SHE WERE A LITTLE
MORE INDEPENDENT.
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
( humming )
- ( wind whooshing )
WHOA. I CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER
THE LAST TIME I FELT SO RELAXED.
- ( Ashley clears throat )
EXCUSE ME.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU WOULDN'T
MIND ME JOINING YOU FOR A BIT.
- REALLY?
SO, WHAT IS AN ELITE
FROM THE R.U.C.
DOING IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
- ( laughs ) I TAKE
IT FROM YOUR TONE
THAT YOU'RE NOT A BIG FAN
OF THE R.U.C, ARE YOU?
- UH, DUH!
BESIDES, THERE ARE PLENTY
OF OTHER PLACES TO SIT HERE.
- OH, DEAR. WELL, THE PROBLEM IS
THAT THIS IS THE ONLY BENCH
THAT'S COMFORTABLE ENOUGH
FOR ME TO TAKE A NAP ON.
IF I DON'T GET A GOOD
NAP IN, I'M AFRAID
I RUN THE TERRIBLE
RISK OF FALLING ASLEEP
WHILE I'M ON DUTY.
I GOT IN SO MUCH TROUBLE
THE LAST TIME THAT HAPPENED.
IF IT HAPPENS AGAIN,
WHO KNOWS WHAT THEY'LL DO.
- ( chuckles ) YOU'RE
AN ODD ONE, HUH?
ALL RIGHT. YOU CAUGHT ME
IN A GOOD MOOD TODAY.
I'LL MAKE AN EXCEPTION.
HAVE A SEAT.
- WELL, AS LONG AS
YOU DON'T MIND.
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
- SO WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS WRONG WITH YOU?
I MEAN WHAT KIND OF
R.U.C. ELITE WOULD CHOOSE
TO TAKE A NAP
IN SUCH A STRANGE PLACE?
- IS IT REALLY SO STRANGE?
I HAPPEN TO THINK
IT'S A VERY NICE PLACE,
ESPECIALLY TODAY,
UNDER SUCH A BEAUTIFUL SKY,
SUCH A BEAUTIFUL LADY.
UM, LISTEN, FLATTERY WON'T GET
YOU ANYWHERE WITH ME, OKAY?
- THERE'S NO ULTERIOR
MOTIVE HERE.
I JUST CAN'T HELP
BUT FIND YOU TO BE
A VERY BEAUTIFUL
AND ATTRACTIVE YOUNG WOMAN.
WHEN I FIRST SAW YOU,
WHAT WERE YOU LOOKING AT?
THOSE SHIMMERING EYES,
WHAT ARE THEY SEARCHING FOR?
- LISTEN, BUDDY,
DON'T EVEN THINK THAT
CRAP'S GONNA WORK WITH ME.
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I'VE GOT MORE
IMPORTANT THINGS TO DO.
- WELL, I HOPE TO
SEE YOU AGAIN SOON!
- UGH. WHAT A JERK!
WHO DOES HE
THINK HE IS, ANYWAY?
WHAT IS WITH EVERYBODY TODAY?
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR YOUR OBJECTIONS.
JUST SIGN THIS CONTRACT!
( gasps )
- AND STAY OUT!
- THAT HAS GOT TO BE
THE MOST THICK-HEADED
--OLD MAN IN THE ENTIRE WORLD!
- HE SAID "NO" AGAIN?
- ( sighs ) TOMORROW'LL BE
MY LAST CHANCE.
ALRIGHT, I THINK I NEED TO
TRY A DIFFERENT APPROACH.
( sighs )
WHAT IS IT, OLD MAN? EXACTLY
WHAT PART OF THE AGREEMENT
DO YOU HAVE A PROBLEM WITH?
IF YOU TELL ME, THERE
MIGHT BE ROOM TO NEGOTIATE.
- SOLTY WON'T BE A THIEF
AND THAT'S FINAL.
- NOW YOU LISTEN TO ME.
WE MAY BE THIEVES, BUT WHAT
WE DO IS FOR THE GOOD OF...
- A CRIMINAL IS A CRIMINAL!
- AH. SO, THAT'S HOW IT IS.
- UH, ROSE. MAYBE YOU SHOULD...
THAT'S WHAT YOU
THINK ABOUT ME.
YOU HAVEN'T HEARD A WORD I'VE
SAID TO YOU THIS WHOLE TIME!
I'VE JUST BEEN
WASTING MY BREATH!
- IT'S USELESS.
FINE THEN, IF YOU DON'T
WANNA SEE THINGS MY WAY,
I'LL JUST GET WHAT I WANT
BY FORCE.
- GIVE IT YOUR BEST SHOT, GIRL.
- MAYBE YOU SHOULD...
- ( gun cocks )
- NO, DON'T! ROSE! PLEASE!
ROSE, NO! DON'T DO THIS!
- YOU IDIOT!
- ( shot fires )
- NO! DAMNIT!
HE'S GETTING AWAY! COME BACK!
HE'S STILL ALIVE!
NO, IT'S NOT... NOT POSSIBLE.
HOW COULD HE?
IT CAN'T BE REAL! IT CAN'T!!
- WHAT? ROSE, WHO?
- DAMN HIM! DAMN HIM!
- Miranda: SO, HOW'S ROSE DOING?
- WELL, SHE SEEMS TO HAVE
CALMED DOWN FOR NOW.
IT'S JUST SO HARD TO BELIEVE,
POOR ROSE FALLING APART AND
LOSING CONTROL LIKE SHE DID.
- SO, DID YOU SEE THIS GUY?
THIS MYSTERIOUS PERSON ROSE
WAS CARRYING ON ABOUT?
- NO. I DIDN'T SEE HIM.
- THAT'S SO ODD.
OKAY, LET'S TAKE A LOOK IN
THE CITY'S ANTI-CRIME DATABASE.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
WE WERE ON THE SIDEWALK
NEAR 35 MEMPHIS BOULEVARD,
AROUND 1545.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
- LOTS OF CAMERAS IN THAT AREA.
MM. THERE'S TONS OF THEM,
A LOT TO GO THROUGH.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE US A WHILE
TO IDENTIFY HIM. IF ONLY THERE
WERE AN EASIER WAY FOR US
TO SINGLE OUT THE SUSPECT.
- THERE IS.
- ROSE! FEELING ANY BETTER?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- DON'T TRY TO STOP ME.
THIS IS MY PROBLEM.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
SO JUST STAY OUT OF MY WAY.
- ROSE! HOLD ON!
- Larry: WELL, WELL,
MR. ROY REVANT. I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU WENT THROUGH ALL THIS
TROUBLE TO HUNT US DOWN.
- YEAH, WELL, IT WASN'T
ALL THAT HARD.
- WHAT? IDIOT!
SHE PRINTED OUT
ALL OUR CONTACT INFORMATION!
- SO TELL ME, WHAT IS IT
YOU WANT FROM US?
- DO YOU RECOGNIZE ANYONE
IN THESE PHOTOS?
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- HE CAN'T BE ALIVE!
- WHO'S STILL ALIVE?
ANSWER ME!
WHOEVER IT IS MADE HER GO OUT
OF HER MIND WHEN SHE SAW HIM!
- Larry: JOHN KIMBERLY.
ABOUT EIGHT OR NINE YEARS AGO,
HE BRUTALLY MURDERED ROSE'S
BEST FRIEND AND HER PARENTS.
IT ALL HAPPENED
RIGHT IN FRONT OF HER.
- WHAT?
- John: DO YOU, UH, WANT
SOMETHING FROM ME, YOUNG LADY?
SEEMS THAT YOU'VE BEEN
FOLLOWING ME FOR SOME TIME.
- DOES THE NAME
IRENE HAYES RING A BELL?
- EH, NO. SHOULD IT?
- YES. IT'S THE
NAME OF THE GIRL
YOU MURDERED EIGHT YEARS
AGO, YOU SON OF A BITCH!
- EASY, EASY. YOU
SHOULDN'T GO AROUND
POINTING A DANGEROUS
THING LIKE THAT.
I THINK YOU'VE MADE A MISTAKE!
- DON'T GIMME THAT CRAP!
IT'S NO MISTAKE!
I'LL NEVER FORGET THAT FACE.
- MY DEAR GIRL,
I HONESTLY DON'T REMEMBER
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
I MEAN HOW COULD I
WHEN I'VE KILLED SO MANY
PEOPLE OVER THE YEARS.
YOU SEE, WHEN I
NEEDED MONEY, I KILLED.
WHEN I NEEDED FOOD, I KILLED.
YOU CAN'T EXPECT ME
TO REMEMBER THEM ALL.
ESPECIALLY JUST
ONE LITTLE GIRL.
- ( shots firing )
- A DEFLECTIVE SHIELD?
- SORRY, BUT IT'S AGAINST
MY PERSONAL POLICY
TO LET ANY WITNESSES LIVE!
- KIMBERLY IS A CUNNING MAN.
HE ONLY MURDERS
UNREGISTERED CITIZENS.
BUT HE, HIMSELF,
IS AN UNREGISTERED CITIZEN.
AND THE POLICE HAVE A TENDENCY
TO OVERLOOK SUCH CASES.
- THAT BASTARD! I HEARD THAT
HE'D FINALLY BEEN KILLED!
- WELL, IF ROSE FINDS HIM,
THE ONLY THING THAT SHE'LL
HAVE ON HER MIND IS REVENGE.
- WE'VE GOTTA HURRY! WE
GOTTA STOP HER BEFORE SHE...
- RIGHT.
- ( phone ringing )
- HELLO?
- Roy: KASHA. IT'S ME.
LEMME TALK TO ROSE.
- ROSE LEFT!
SHE LOOKED CRAZY!
SHE SAID "STAY OUT OF
MY WAY" AND TOOK OFF.
SOLTY JUST RAN OUT
TO TELL YOU GUYS!
- OKAY, JUST CALM DOWN.
- Solty: ROY!
- SOLTY!
- ROY!
- (shots firing )
- A GUN IS USELESS AGAINST ME!
- I HAVE TO... SHOOT THE FLESH.
- ( metallic crashing )
- YOU UNDERESTIMATE ME, GIRL!
- GAME OVER, KIMBERLY.
- YOU SURE?
- ( shots firing )
- ( shot fires )
- OH, MY...
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
GUESS I GOT CARRIED AWAY.
YOU HAD ENOUGH?
GIVE IT UP.
YOU'LL NEVER BEAT ME!
AND REMEMBER...
I DON'T LIKE TO LEAVE
ANY WITNESSES.
SO...
( chuckling )
ROSE! HEY! ROSE!
- SOUNDED LIKE A GUN SHOT.
- OVER THERE!
- YEAH.
- OH, NO!
ROSE, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
SAY SOMETHING!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
JUST STAY OUT OF THIS!
DON'T YOU GET IT?
HE KILLED MY BEST FRIEND.
MY ONLY FRIEND.
IRENE MEANT EVERYTHING TO ME.
CAN'T YOU AT LEAST
TRY TO UNDERSTAND THIS.
WE PLAYED TOGETHER
AND TALKED ABOUT EVERYTHING!
MY BEST FRIEND.
AND HE JUST SLIT HER THROAT,
RIGHT THERE IN FRONT OF ME.
THERE WAS NOTHING I COULD DO.
I WAS TOO WEAK TO STOP HIM!
I WAS... I WAS USELESS.
THIS CITY... THE LAWS AREN'T
MEANT TO PROTECT US.
THEY'RE MEANT TO KEEP US
UNDER CONTROL.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
THAT'S WHY I DO THE THINGS I DO.
FOR THEM! TO PROTECT
ALL THE UNREGISTERED CITIZENS!
SO WHAT IF I DO IT
BY BEING A THIEF!
IT'S BETTER THAN SITTING AROUND
DOING NOTHING.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE TO HAVE TO
GO THROUGH WHAT I WENT THOUGH.
NEVER. NEVER AGAIN!
( crying )
- ROSE, I...
UH, ROY...
- THERE'S NO CHOICE.
YOU THINK YOU CAN FIND HIM?
- JUST LEAVE IT TO ME.
- ( breathing deeply )
LOOKS LIKE HER FRIENDS
ARE HERE...
- ( explosion booms )
- I DON'T LIKE YOU.
- WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT ARE YOU?
- THAT WON'T WORK ON ME!
( screams )
( grunting )
- ROSE, WAIT!
- FINALLY.
- NO! NO, DON'T!
PLEASE DON'T KILL ME!
HELP ME! SOMEBODY STOP HER!
- JUST SHUT UP!
SHUT UP! SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
IRENE BEGGED FOR HER LIFE, TOO,
JUST LIKE THAT.
AND YOU MURDERED HER ANYWAY!
YOU DESERVE TO DIE!
- ROSE! STOP IT!
- NO!
- DON'T DO IT!
- John: SOMEBODY! PLEASE!
- ROSE!
- ( whimpering )
PLEASE! I DON'T WANNA DIE!
HELP ME!
- ROSE.
- ROSE! NO!
- ( sobbing )
( screams )
- Larry: SORRY IF WE
INCONVENIENCED YOU.
- IF YOU'RE REALLY SORRY,
THEN WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
HER HOME WITH YOU?
- AW, COME ON ROY.
I DON'T HAVE THE HEART
TO WAKE HER UP.
BESIDES, THIS COULD
WORK OUT IN YOUR FAVOR.
WITH ALL OF OUR INSIDE
CONNECTIONS
WE MIGHT FIND EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
- AND WHY SHOULD I
TRUST YOU? HMM?
- YOU SAW WHAT WE DID HERE.
YOU KNOW YOU CAN TRUST US.
AND PARTNERING UP
WITH A HUNTER
IS QUITE AN APPEALING
OPPORTUNITY FOR US, AS WELL.
- SUIT YOURSELF, THEN.
LATER.
- ( gun cocks )
- ( gasps )
NO, NO, NO!
- ( gun shot fires )
- ( closing theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sylvia: HEY!
WHO IS THAT GIRL?
- Celica: I DON'T KNOW.
WHO COULD SHE BE?
- Integra: WHAT'RE YOU TWO
DOING OVER THERE?
- All: NEXT EPISODE,
GIRLS' DAY OFF!
- MY WORK HERE IS DONE.