- Integra: I'M GOING OUT.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO CHECK ON.
- INTEGRA?
- DO YOU THINK YOU CAN PUT THIS
TOGETHER IN ONE DAY, AXELA?
- SURE, SHOULDN'T BE
TOO MUCH OF A PROBLEM.
- GOOD, THEN I'LL
LEAVE YOU TO IT.
I SHOULD BE BACK BY THEN, OKAY?
- HEY, WAIT. I'LL GO WITH YOU.
- I'M COUNTING ON YOU.
- NO, WAIT.
- ( door closes )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- MIRANDA, I NEVER
EXPECTED TO SEE YOU HERE.
- ( chuckles ) I COULD SAY
THE SAME. HOW ARE YOU, ROSE?
HONESTLY, IT WAS A
BIT OF A SHOCK
TO US TO HEAR THAT YOU
WERE WORKING FOR R.U.C.,
I MEAN, CONSIDERING
YOUR PAST AND ALL.
- WELL, A LOT HAS CHANGED.
- SO, WHEN ARE YOU
COMING BACK HOME, DEAR?
THE APARTMENT IS FAIRLY CLOSE,
SO, IT SHOULD BE
AN EASY COMMUTE.
WHEN YOU LEFT, EVERYONE
WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
ESPECIALLY ROY. WHY DON'T
YOU STOP BY TONIGHT,
JUST TO SHOW
EVERYONE YOU'RE OKAY?
COME ON, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- SORRY, MIRANDA.
I WON'T BE GOING BACK
THERE ANYTIME SOON.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I HAVE WORK TO DO.
- BUT, ROSE, WAIT.
HMM. HUH?
( gasps )
- Andy: OH, I SEE THEM NOW.
CRAWLING ALL OVER THE PLACE.
- Roy: R.U.C.?
- OH, YEAH.
- ROSE TIPPED ME OFF ABOUT
THEM THIS MORNING, ROY.
- IF THEY'RE OUT THERE,
IT CAN ONLY MEAN,
THEY'RE LOOKING
FOR INTEGRA AND AXELA.
QUESTION IS HOW DID
THEY KNOW WHERE TO LOOK?
- ( sighs ) DAMN IT, I GUESS,
THAT'D BE MY FAULT.
- YOU, ROY?
- WHAT'D YOU DO? YOU TRYING
TO GET US ALL KILLED, OLD MAN?
- SAVE THE FINGER-POINTING
FOR LATER.
RIGHT NOW, WE JUST NEED TO
KNOW WHAT BROUGHT THEM HERE,
SO WE CAN FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO DO NEXT.
- IF R.U.C. SECURITY
IS OUT THERE
WATCHING EVERYTHING WE DO,
DOES THAT MEAN WE CAN'T
GO ANYWHERE? AM I GOING TO
HAVE TO MISS SCHOOL AGAIN?
- NO, THINK ABOUT IT,
IF THEY REALLY KNEW
INTEGRA AND AXELA WERE HERE,
I DOUBT THEY'D BE
WAITING OUTSIDE.
THEY COULD HAVE EASILY
STORMED THIS PLACE HOURS AGO
BUT FOR SOME REASON, THEY
HAVEN'T. IF I HAD TO GUESS,
IT SOUNDS LIKE THEY STILL
DON'T HAVE ENOUGH EVIDENCE
TO JUSTIFY MOVING IN.
- SO, LET'S NOT GIVE THEM ANY,
IS WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- SO, WHAT THE HECK
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
- JUST ACT NORMALLY.
- IF WE DO ANYTHING
THAT LOOKS SUSPICIOUS,
IT COULD BE ALL THE
REASON THEY NEED
TO COME SEARCH THIS PLACE.
- YEAH, BUT STILL,
DON'T LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
IT'S PROBABLY SAFE TO ASSUME
THEY'RE TAPPING THE PHONES
AND READING THE MAIL.
- JOSEPH SAID HE WAS SENDING
US A PACKAGE.
- RIGHT.
- I'LL GO TO THE POST OFFICE
AND MAKE A REQUEST THAT
THEY HOLD ALL OUR MAIL.
COME ON, KASHA. LET'S GO.
- NOW, AS FOR AXELA
AND INTEGRA THEMSELVES.
- WHERE'S INTEGRA?
- UH, YOU SEE, SHE, UH...
- DID SHE LEAVE?
- WELL, UM SHE SAID THAT, UH...
- SOLTY!
- UH, SHE SAID
SHE'D BE BACK SOON.
- WHERE'D SHE GO?
- WE NEED TO KNOW, SPIT IT OUT.
- SHE ASKED ME ABOUT JOSEPH,
SO, I TOLD HER WHERE
HE LIVED. THEN SHE...
- AND HE'S THE GUY WHO LEFT
THE MESSAGE ABOUT THE PACKAGE?
- THAT'S HIM. BUT WHY WOULD
SHE GO OUT TO HIS PLACE?
- ( gasps )
- MAN, I DON'T GET IT.
WHY COULDN'T THE OLD GUY
CHECK THIS OUT HIMSELF?
- ( gadget beeps )
- BEATS ME. JUST KEEP
FOLLOWING THIS ROAD, OKAY?
- YEAH, I KNOW AND WHY'D
HE HAVE TO STICK ME WITH YOU?
- MAYBE HE WAS WORRIED YOU
COULDN'T HANDLE IT BY YOURSELF.
- SHUT UP, YOU GEEK.
- Yuto: KEEP YOUR EYES
ON THE ROAD.
- OKAY, THEN. YOU WANT US TO
STOP ALL MAIL FOR MR. ROY REVANT
AND HOLD IT HERE, HUH?
- YES. HE'S ALSO
EXPECTING A PACKAGE,
WE'LL BE PICKING UP LATER.
- HIS ADDRESS IS...
- ALREADY HAVE IT, MA'AM. 2015
CONNAGER STREET , RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
SOMEONE CAME IN EARLIER
ASKING FOR THE SAME THING.
FRIEND OF YOURS, MAYBE.
ANYWAY, I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT I TOLD THEM.
PACKAGES THAT ARRIVED LAST NIGHT
HAVE ALREADY GONE
OUT ON THE TRUCKS,
SO, IT'S TOO LATE TO STOP THEM.
SORRY, MA'AM.
- Integra: SO, THIS IS IT.
- Man: ASHLEY LYNX?
- Roy: YEAH, OPERATION DIRECTOR.
- THE R.U.C. DIRECTOR
I'VE SEEN ON THE NEWS?
THE ONE HANDLING
THAT MURDER CASE?
- YOU THINK HE'S DIRTY?
- JUST CHECK HIM OUT
FOR ME, SEE WHAT TURNS UP.
- YEAH, SEEMS LIKE YOUR TYPICAL
R.U.C. ELITE, YOU ASK ME.
- OH, NO. TRUST ME, THERE'S
NOTHING TYPICAL ABOUT THIS GUY.
ANYWAY, START ASKING AROUND.
I WANT TO KNOW EVERYTHING
THERE IS TO KNOW ABOUT HIM.
- YEAH, YEAH. HOW CAN I SAY NO
WHEN YOU ASK ME SO NICE?
- THANKS.
- I OWE YOU ONE.
- ( gasps )
- I WISH THERE WAS
SOMETHING MORE
I COULD DO TO HELP RIGHT NOW.
BUT FOOD ALWAYS SEEMS
TO MAKE PEOPLE FEEL BETTER.
SO, I'LL MAKE THEM
A GOOD DINNER TONIGHT.
- Ashley: EXCUSE ME.
- YEAH?
CAN I HELP YOU?
- IT'S BEEN A WHILE, DIIKE.
- DIIKE?
- HAS TO BE IT.
( grunting )
( panting )
THIS IS IT.
THERE'S NO MISTAKING IT.
THIS WAS THE PROCEED
RESEARCH LAB.
IT'S WHERE THEY
WORKED ON US.
- Yuto: SO, TELL ME.
- Andy: WHAT?
- Yuto: BE HONEST. YOU'VE GOT
A THING FOR ROSE, DON'T YOU?
- WHAT? WHAT THE HELL
WOULD GIVE YOU THAT IDEA?
- OH, IT'S JUST A LITTLE HUNCH.
SEEMS LIKE ALL SOMEONE
HAS TO DO IS MENTION HER NAME,
AND YOU BREAK OUT
IN A SWEAT, LIKE NOW.
- SO, WHAT IF I DO HAVE
A THING FOR HER?
WE'RE NOT BLOOD RELATIVES.
- I REST MY CASE.
- SHUT YOUR TRAP,
YOU FREAKING NERD.
- Kasha: SOLTY'S SURE IS TAKING
A LONG TIME AT THE MARKET, HUH?
- ( laughs ) OH, I'M SURE SHE'S
JUST HAVING TROUBLE DECIDING
WHAT TO MAKE FOR DINNER.
- GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT. HUH?
- ( both gasp )
- S... SOLTY?
( screams ) SOLTY!
- Andy: GREAT. SO, WHAT NOW?
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSE
TO EXPLAIN THIS? COME ON.
- WE'LL TELL THE TRUTH. IT WAS
LIKE THIS WHEN WE GOT HERE.
WE FOUND THE COTTAGE AND IT
WAS ALL BLOWN TO SMITHEREENS,
AND THERE WAS NO SIGN
OF INTEGRA, ANYWHERE.
- Ashley: HOW'S YOUR PROGRESS?
- Researcher: SLOW.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE TIME
TO ADJUST EVERY NERVE.
- HOW LONG?
- TWELVE HOURS. PERHAPS LONGER.
- WHERE WERE YOU?
- THERE WAS SOME BUSINESS
THAT REQUIRED MY ATTENTION.
NOW THAT IT'S RESOLVED,
YOU'RE MY ONLY CONCERN.
- I SEE.
- GET SOME REST NOW.
WHEN YOU AWAKEN NEXT,
OUR GRAND ENDEAVOR BEGINS.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
ALL OF YOUR STRENGTH.
- YES, REST SOUNDS GOOD.
- TELL ME, JUST HOW
FEASIBLE IS BRAINWASHING?
- WE COULD TRY IT, SIR,
BUT THERE'S THE POTENTIAL
FOR SIDE EFFECTS.
THERE'S A CHANCE, IT
COULD INTERFERE
WITH HER PROCEED ABILITIES.
- YES, I SEE.
- SOLTY.
( gasps ) WHA,
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
- WHEN WE FOUND HER,
SHE WAS ALREADY LIKE THAT.
- SHE'S NOT DEAD, IS SHE, ROY?
IS SHE? ROY?
- ( sobs ) NO, SHE CAN'T BE.
DAMMIT, ISN'T THERE ANYONE
AROUND HERE THAT CAN FIX HER?
- I'M SORRY.
I JUST WASN'T EVER TRAINED
AS A RESEMBLE TECHNICIAN.
- IF YUTO WAS HERE, HE MIGHT BE
ABLE TO DO SOMETHING.
- ( sobs )
- ( doorbell rings )
- HOLD ON A SECOND.
OH, I'M SORRY, CAN I HELP YOU?
- IF ROY REVANT IS HERE,
YOU CAN TELL HIM,
JOSEPH IS HERE TO SEE HIM.
- HOW IS SHE?
- BAD, I'M AFRAID. I SUSPECT
THIS IS ASHLEY'S DOING.
- ASHLEY?
- I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN REPAIR HER,
BUT I CAN AT LEAST
TAKE A LOOK.
- JUST... JUST DO IT.
- ROY, HOW DO WE KNOW
WE CAN TRUST THAT GUY?
- WE DON'T EXACTLY
HAVE A CHOICE, DO WE?
- Axela: THAT THING IS NOT
GOING TO PUT ITSELF TOGETHER.
- Integra: AXELA.
- INTEGRA, HOW'D YOU GET INSIDE?
THOSE LOOKOUTS,
THEY'RE EVERYWHERE.
- DON'T WORRY.
I JUST PUT THOSE GUYS TO
SLEEP FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- TO SLEEP? BUT,
IF ANYONE NOTICES...
- HERE, ROY SHOULD BE
EXPECTING THIS PACKAGE.
NOT SURE WHAT IT IS,
BUT IT'S OF NO USE TO ME.
PLEASE GIVE IT TO HIM, OKAY?
NOW, DO YOU HAVE WHAT I NEED?
- OH, RIGHT IT'S
ALMOST FINISHED.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
CONNECT THE FINAL CORD,
AND YOU'RE GOOD TO GO.
- THANKS, BUT DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT. I CAN DO IT MYSELF.
- UM, NO WAIT. PLEASE TAKE
ME WITH YOU, INTEGRA.
LET'S, LET'S
WORK TOGETHER.
- HUH. AXELA.
- INTEGRA, I'M COMING.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
HURRY UP AND GET READY.
- ( sighs ) THANKS.
- I HOPE YOU'LL
FORGIVE ME, AXELA.
- HUH?
- COMPLETELY BURNED OUT.
BUT STILL, BETTER THIS CHIP
THAN THE REST OF
YOUR CIRCUITRY, HUH?
I GUESS WE SHOULD BE
THANKFUL IT WASN'T WORSE.
THIS ISN'T A FACTORY
PART, LITTLE ONE,
BUT HOPEFULLY, IT WILL
GET YOU UP AND RUNNING.
SOLTY? ARE YOU CONSCIOUS?
- SOLTY? NOT RECOGNIZED.
MY NAME IS DIIKE.
- HUH? IT CAN'T BE.
- I HAVE BEEN SENT TO THE
SURFACE FOR THE PURPOSE OF...
- ( buzzes )
- HUH?
- SHE OKAY?
- I HAVE NEITHER
THE RIGHT PARTS,
NOR THE TOOLS TO
REPAIR HER HERE.
- DAMMIT.
- HEY, WHERE IS SHE? THE GIRL,
THE ONE WITH THE SHORT HAIR.
WHERE DID SHE GO?
- ( gasps )
- ( tires screeching )
- HUH? RUN FOR YOUR LIFE.
- HEY, WHAT'S WITH THE SMOKE?
- IT'S COMING FROM
THE R.U.C. BUILDING.
- ( beeping )
- YES, WHAT IS IT?
- Man: A SECTION 7
COMMAND VEHICLE
JUST CRASHED INTO
THE LOBBY, SIR.
- WHAT?
- Man: WE'VE SECURED
THE VEHICLE,
BUT THE DRIVER HAS
FLED INTO THE BUILDING.
WE ARE IN PURSUIT AT THIS TIME.
- ( beeping )
- SIR, UH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY YOU ARE
ACTIVATING YOUR TRANSPONDER?
- WE DON'T WANT OUR GUEST
GETTING LOST, NOW, DO WE?
I SHOULD GO WELCOME HER.
- ( siren wailing )
- GOT IT.
- Roy: HEY, HEY, WAKE UP.
- HEY, WHAT'S THIS? IS THIS THE
PACKAGE WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR?
THIS IS IT, RIGHT?
- HMM.
- BUT HOW IN THE WORLD
COULD IT HAVE GOTTEN HERE?
- YOU OKAY, WHAT HAPPENED?
- WHERE'S INTEGRA?
- INTEGRA, WHERE IS SHE?
- INTEGRA?
- AH, THEN I GUESS
THAT MAKES YOU AXELA.
- WAIT, HOW DO YOU KNOW THESE
GIRLS? WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
JOSEPH, TALK.
- ( beeping )
- COME ON, WORK FOR ME.
- Joseph: THESE GIRLS
ARE PROCEED.
I WAS THE SCIENTIST
WHO AUGMENTED THEM
YEARS AGO AT R.U.C.
THE PROCEED ARE A
NEW CLASS OF HUMANS,
CREATED BY THE BLAST FALL.
WHEN IT HAPPENED, DROPLETS OF
LIGHT RAINED DOWN UPON THE CITY.
THESE DROPLETS, THEY WERE
ACTUALLY THE NANOMACHINES
THAT FORM THE AURORA SHELL.
- NANOMACHINES?
- Joseph: MACHINES THE
SIZE OF MOLECULES.
- SO SMALL, THEY'RE INVISIBLE
TO THE NAKED EYE.
- HUH?
- IT SEEMS, FOR CERTAIN YOUNG
GIRLS EXPOSED TO THE BLAST FALL,
THE ABSORPTION OF
THESE NANOMACHINES
HAD A DNA ALTERING EFFECT.
WE DUBBED THESE GIRLS
PROCEED. THEY'RE SUPERHUMAN.
EACH ONE OF THEM MANIFESTING
DISTINCT SPECIAL ABILITIES.
SOME POSSESS ENHANCED
STRENGTH AND SPEED,
FOR OTHERS, IT WAS ENHANCED
VISION AND REFLEXES.
SOME DEVELOPED SUPERIOR
INTELLIGENCE. THEY'RE PERFECT.
BUT THE STRESS
ON THEIR BODIES IS HUGE.
AS A RESULT, THEIR BODIES
HAVE TO BE AUGMENTED
WITH ENHANCEMENTS TO SURVIVE.
- SO, HOW DOES AN OLD MAN
LIKE YOU KNOW ALL THIS?
- I GREW WEARY OF MY ROLE
AND BECAME A BIT OF AN OBSERVER.
- WHAT THE HECK
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- HOLD ON,
IF I HEARD YOU CORRECTLY,
THEN, NANOMACHINES THINGS
MAKE UP THE AURORA SHELL?
IS THE AURORA SHELL MAN-MADE?
- HMM.
- WHAT DO WE NEED IT FOR?
- THE AURORA SHELL IS A MEMBRANE
THAT CONTAINS A
BREATHABLE ATMOSPHERE,
NECESSARY SINCE THIS
PLANET ORIGINALLY
HAD NO AIR OF ITS OWN.
- NO AIR? ARE YOU
REALLY SERIOUS?
- VERY MUCH SO, YOUNG LADY.
- WITHOUT THE AURORA SHELL,
WE COULDN'T LIVE HERE.
THAT'S WHY WE, HUMANS,
BUILT IT WHEN WE MOVED
HERE TO THIS PLANET.
- ( all gasp )
- WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
- IT'S A SHIP OF HOPE. MY SHIP.
MY MEANS OF ESCAPING
THIS DESPICABLE PLANET.
TRUE, THE FIRST ONE
FAILED, BUT THIS ONE WON'T.
I'VE REMEDIED THE MISTAKES
I MADE TWELVE YEARS AGO.
- TWELVE YEARS? SO, IT WAS YOU.
THE BLAST FALL WAS
YOUR FAULT, WASN'T IT?
- AH, IT SEEMS YOU'VE BEEN
DOING YOUR HOMEWORK.
- I HAD THE FEELING,
SOMETHING WAS ROTTEN.
EVER SINCE THE DAY
OF THE CLOCK TOWER DISASTER.
YOU ORDERED ME
TO RESCUE ROSE. WHY?
- PROCEED REPRESENT THE FUTURE
OF HUMANITY FOR THIS WORLD.
THE OTHERS OUT THERE,
RESEMBLE DRONES,
ALL OF THEM SLAVES TO
THOSE WICKED WITCHES,
WE CALL MACHINES. I NEEDED
YOU AND YOUR ABILITIES TO
HELP ME "BREAK THE
SPELL", SO TO SPEAK.
- WHAT IN THE HELL ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT? EXPLAIN YOURSELF.
- NO, NO, IT HARDLY MATTERS.
YOU, INTEGRA HAVE
OUTLIVED YOUR USEFULNESS.
- SO, ALL THIS TIME,
WE'VE JUST BEEN TOOLS TO YOU,
TO BE USED AND THROWN
AWAY AT YOUR CONVENIENCE,
IS THAT WHAT YOU MEAN?
SILVIA, SHE, SHE WAS MY FRIEND,
A CLOSE FRIEND. AND CELICA.
SHE COULD BE HANDFUL SOMETIMES,
BUT WE ALL LOVED HER.
THEY WERE MY FAMILY.
SO, I'M DOING THIS FOR THEM NOW,
YOU BASTARD.
- OH, SUCH FOOLISH EMOTION.
- ( grunts )
- AH, YES, OVERCLOCK.
THE ABILITY TO PERFORM MOMENTARY
BURSTS OF HIGH-SPEED MOVEMENT.
HOWEVER, IT'S
QUITE TAXING, ISN'T IT?
IF MEMORY SERVES ME CORRECTLY,
IT INDUCES A MASSIVE STRAIN
ON YOUR CEREBRAL CORTEX.
IT CAN ONLY BE USED
THREE TIMES, AM I RIGHT?
ANY MORE AND YOUR BODY
COMPLETELY SHUTS DOWN.
AND YOU'VE ONLY GOT
TWO LEFT, INTEGRA.
- ( gasps )
- IT CAN'T BE EASY.
KNOWING THAT YOU'RE ONLY
DESTROYING YOURSELF,
WITH EACH WASTED ATTACK.
- SHUT UP.
- JUST ONE LEFT. BUT,
I'LL MAKE YOU A DEAL, INTEGRA.
STOP NOW, AND I PROMISE YOU,
YOUR DEATH WILL
BE A PAINLESS ONE.
- NEVER.
( screams )
- OH, NICE TRY.
- NO, HOW DID...
( screams )
( groans )
- NOW, THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU DON'T UNDERGO
REGULAR MAINTENANCE.
YOU PROCEED REALLY ARE
A DELICATE LITTLE
LOT, AREN'T YOU, NOW?
THIS VOLTAGE WAS ENOUGH TO
PUT DIIKE OUT OF COMMISSION
WITH ONE STRIKE.
IT'LL BE MORE THAN
ENOUGH FOR YOU.
- SILVIA. CELICA.
- YOUR TIME'S UP, INTEGRA.
- ( shouting )
- ( screams )
- AH, A FOURTH OVERCLOCK.
I'M IMPRESSED.
TOO BAD, MY RESEMBLE COMPONENTS
ARE OF A HIGHER QUALITY
THAN THOSE FOUND
ON THE AVERAGE CITIZEN.
- DAMMIT.
( screams )
- STILL ALIVE? BUT YOUR BODY
AND MIND ARE BROKEN.
IN ANY CASE, YOU'LL
MAKE THE PERFECT BAIT
TO LURE AXELA OUT OF HIDING.
- I WON'T FORGIVE YOU,
FOR WHAT YOU HAVE DONE.
ASHLEY LYNX,
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( music playing )
- Joseph: SO,
WHERE SHOULD I START?
- Axela: IT'S BECAUSE
I WAS THAT WAY, TOO.
- Solty: NEXT TIME,
"THE TIME FOR TRUTH."
WHO ARE YOU PEOPLE?