- ( footsteps approaching )
- Will: WHAT IS THAT?
HELLO? HELLO?
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
HEY GRAMPS. I FOUND
A GIRL OVER HERE.
I THINK SHE'S STILL ALIVE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ALL RIGHT. THAT SHOULD DO
IT FOR YOUR PAPERWORK.
GOOD LUCK TONIGHT.
- THANKS.
- ( keyboard clacking )
- YUTO.
HAVE YOU FOUND ANYTHING
ON SOLTY, YET?
- NO, NOTHING YET.
THE SURVEILLANCE
CAMERAS CAME UP EMPTY.
- OH.
- BUT I'LL EXPAND MY SEARCH
PARAMETERS A LITTLE MORE.
- YES, PLEASE DO.
AND THANKS FOR WORKING ALL
NIGHT. I KNOW IT'S HARD.
- LEAST I CAN DO.
- KASHA, SHOULDN'T YOU BE
LEAVING FOR SCHOOL SOON?
- YEAH. I'D BETTER GET GOING.
- KASHA, WOULD YOU LIKE IT
IF I WALKED YOU TO SCHOOL
THIS MORNING? I HAVE
TO GET SOMETHING
AT THE STORE, AND
IT'S ON THE WAY,
SO I FIGURED WE
COULD, YOU KNOW...
- I'M NOT A BABY.
I CAN GO MYSELF.
THE ONLY THING YOU SHOULD
BE WORRIED ABOUT RIGHT NOW
IS FINDING SOLTY.
- I GUESS SHE'S TAKING THIS
PRETTY HARD, TOO, AND ROY...
- I'M GETTING HUNGRY.
- ( clattering )
- HOW COULD I LET THIS
HAPPEN TO RITA?
( crying ) I'M SO SORRY
I COULDN'T SAVE YOU.
- WHERE AM I?
ROY! WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WAIT, ROY.
WHY WON'T YOU ANSWER ME?
IS IT BECAUSE I'M A MACHINE?
BECAUSE I'M STILL ALIVE
INSTEAD OF ROSE?
WHAT IF I WERE HUMAN?
WHAT THEN?
ROY, PLEASE!
- SO, YOU'RE AWAKE.
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU
WOKE UP AT ALL.
YOU MANAGED TO OVERSTRESS
A NUMBER OF KEY COMPONENTS.
AND YOUR AI CIRCUITS WERE
ALMOST COMPLETELY OVERLOADED.
IT'S A GOOD THING I HAD SOME
SPARE PARTS LYING AROUND.
- HUH?
- SO, LET'S HEAR YOUR STORY.
- WHAT WAS IT THAT BROUGHT
YOU TO US, LITTLE ONE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
WHEN DID YOU ARRIVE?
WHAT'S YOUR PURPOSE?
YOU CAN HEAR ME, CAN'T YOU?
HMM, MAYBE HER LANGUAGE
CIRCUITS ARE DAMAGED.
- NO, THEY'RE NOT.
AND PLEASE SIR, DON'T
TALK ABOUT ME LIKE THAT.
- NOW WE'RE GETTING SOMEWHERE.
SO DOES ANYONE KNOW YOU'RE HERE?
YOU NEED TO ANSWER ME.
- I DON'T WANT TO ANSWER YOU.
- I NEVER THOUGHT
IT WAS POSSIBLE.
I BELIEVE YOU'RE SELF-AWARE.
- LISTEN, SINCE YOU REPAIRED ME
I PROMISE I WON'T MAKE
ANY TROUBLE FOR YOU,
SO WOULD YOU MIND
PUTTING THAT GUN AWAY, PLEASE?
IT'S MAKING ME NERVOUS.
IT'S FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY.
I WOULDN'T WANT A BULLET
TO RICOCHET OFF ME
AND HIT YOU BY MISTAKE.
- HMM. I GUESS YOU
HAVE A POINT.
- I'M SORRY I CAN'T
ANSWER YOUR QUESTIONS.
I APPRECIATE YOUR HELP THOUGH.
THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME.
- ( door closes )
- ( sighs )
- HEY THERE.
SO YOU'RE AWAKE, HUH?
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S REALLY GOOD TO SEE YOU
BACK ON YOUR FEET.
FEELIN' ANY BETTER?
YOU GAVE ME A HECK OF A SCARE
OUT THERE WHEN I FOUND YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE A GONER.
ANYWAY, MY NAME'S
WILL. NICE TO MEET YOU.
- UH...
IT'S NICE TO
MEET YOU TOO.
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- UH, IT'S SOLTY.
- SOLTY. COOL.
SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
IT'S NOT LIKE THERE'S ANYTHING
TO DO AROUND THIS PLACE.
WERE YOU ON A HIKE BY YOURSELF?
WOW! THAT'S PRETTY DANGEROUS.
- THIS DESERT WILL
EAT YOU ALIVE, YOU KNOW.
- YOU WERE LUCKY.
JUST SO HAPPENED I WAS
OUT SCAVENGING FOR PARTS
FOR THE PLANE I WAS
BUILDING. WANNA SEE IT?
- UM, I GUESS.
- ( chuckles )
- SO THIS IS WHAT
A PLANE LOOKS LIKE?
- YUP. NEVER SEEN ONE BEFORE?
- NO, I HAVEN'T.
- PRETTY COOL, ISN'T IT?
IT'S A MACHINE THAT
CAN FLY LIKE A BIRD.
- A BIRD?
- LIKE THIS.
( mimics motor sounds )
SHE CAN FLY FAST AND HIGH,
BUT NOT HIGH ENOUGH
TO GET CAUGHT IN THE
ALTITUDE CEILING.
NOT LIKE I'D EVER
WANT TO GO THAT HIGH.
IT WASN'T EASY BUILDING
THIS, YOU KNOW.
PARTS ARE HARD TO COME BY.
YOU CAN'T JUST GO TO A STORE AND
GET WHAT YOU WANT ANYMORE.
I BUILT THIS ENTIRE THING
BY GOING INTO THE CITY
AND SCROUNGING AROUND
FOR WHAT I NEEDED.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WELL, EVERY PART OF THIS BIRD,
FROM THE WINGS TO THE PROPELLER,
IS 100% RECYCLED.
I MADE IT ALL FROM TRASH
I FOUND IN THE CITY.
- SO THIS WAS ALL THROWN AWAY?
- YEAH. IT'S FUNNY 'CAUSE
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
I WAS SORT OF THROWN AWAY
MYSELF. AND GRAMPS THREW AWAY
THE LIFE HE HAD, SO IT'S ALMOST
KINDA FITTING, YOU KNOW?
I'M SO SORRY. I DON'T MEAN
TO TALK YOUR EAR OFF.
- THEN...
- YEAH?
- MAYBE SOMEDAY
IF YOU THINK IT WOULD HELP,
YOU CAN USE ME FOR THIS, TOO.
- CAN I REALLY?
- ( engine roaring )
- ( Will laughing excitedly )
WOW!
THIS IS FANTASTIC.
YOU'RE REALLY STRONG.
- THIS ISN'T WHAT I MEANT
WHEN I SAID YOU COULD USE ME.
- ( exclaims )
- WAIT.
- OKAY. NOW I JUST
HAVE TO STABILIZE
THE AIRFRAME AND THEN...
- ( gasps )
WILL!
WILL, ARE YOU OKAY?
OH NO, PLEASE, NOT AGAIN.
( gasps )
- I FOOLED YOU.
( laughs ) NO REALLY,
I'M OKAY. SEE?
I WAS JUST HAVING
A LITTLE FUN WITH YOU.
SO HEY, YOU CAN GO AHEAD
AND LAUGH NOW, RIGHT?
ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( crying )
- I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO UPSET YOU.
C'MON NOW, DON'T CRY.
I SAID I WAS SORRY.
MAN, SHE WAS ALL CRYING
AND EMOTIONAL, AND THEN
THE NEXT THING I KNEW SHE
JUST COLLAPSED TO THE GROUND.
BUT I DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING TO HER. I SWEAR.
- RELAX. NO ONE'S SAYING
YOU DID ANYTHING WRONG.
- GOOD. AS LONG AS
WE'RE CLEAR ON THAT.
SO, WHO IS THIS GIRL ANYWAY?
YOU KNOW SOMETHING
DON'T YOU, GRAMPS?
- RESPIRATION AND
PULSE ARE STABLE
AND WITHIN THE
ACCEPTABLE PARAMETERS.
- BRAINWAVE LEVEL GREEN.
- READINGS COMPLETE FOR
LINES 72 THROUGH 88.
WE'RE READING A
CONTROL CO-EFFICIENT
OF ZERO POINT SIX FIVE.
PROCESSING SPEED STILL
INCREASING STEADILY.
- SHE'S CONNECTING THE
PROCESSING LINES BY HERSELF.
STRESS CO-EFFICIENT
IS NEGLIGIBLE.
IT'S AS IF SHE'S FEELING
NO CONTROL STRESS AT ALL.
SHE'S A FANTASTIC SPECIMEN, SIR.
WHY DID YOU KEEP HER
FROM US FOR SO LONG.
- HELLO? AXELA?
- OH. HI SILVIA.
- WHAT'S UP?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO BE ON THE PROGRAM TODAY.
- I WAS, BUT IT GOT CANCELED.
- THAT'S ODD.
- SO I UNDERSTAND THE DIRECTOR
ALREADY HAS YOU INVESTIGATING
THE CLOCK TOWER INCIDENT WITH
INTEGRA AND THE OTHERS?
- YEAH, WELL, YOU DID SO
MUCH TO PICK UP THE SLACK
FOR ME WHILE I WAS
IN THE HOSPITAL,
I FIGURE I HAVE TO
WORK DOUBLE-TIME
JUST TO MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- WHAT?
- SILVIA, YOUR MAKEUP.
- UH. OH THAT. IT'S NOTHING.
CELICA MADE ME
PUT IT ON FOR UH...
- ( chuckles ) IT LOOKS GREAT.
- YEAH, RIGHT. LET'S DROP IT.
SO WHAT'S UP WITH YOU?
YOU JUST SEEM KINDA
TALKATIVE TODAY.
- REALLY?
IS IT THAT BAD?
- NO, IT'S JUST UNUSUAL.
- WELL THEN,
I'LL TRY TO BE QUIET.
- NO, IT'S A NICE CHANGE
OF PACE. SEE YOU AROUND.
- ( lighter striking )
- Will: ALL RIGHT GUYS,
TIME TO PIG OUT.
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON THIS
SOUTHWESTERN THEME FOR A WHILE,
SO I HOPE YOU LIKE IT.
- WILL, HOW MANY
TIMES HAVE I TOLD YOU
TO STAY OUT OF THE KITCHEN?
- HOLD ON NOW, GRAMPS,
DON'T JUST JUDGE IT
BY ITS APPEARANCE.
IT'S HOW IT TASTES
THAT COUNTS, RIGHT?
- WHICH IS WHY I STRONGLY
SUGGEST YOU TAKE THIS AWAY
AND BRING OUT THE
USUAL RATION PACKS.
- BUT THAT WOULDN'T BE
HELPFUL TO OUR GUEST,
WHO I'M TRYING TO
HELP FEEL AT HOME.
THERE'S NOTHING TO WORRY
ABOUT. IT'S DELICIOUS.
( retching )
I TOLD YOU NOT TO
LET ME NEAR THE KITCHEN.
- WHEN YOU GONNA LEARN, WILLIAM?
- WAIT A SECOND.
- HUH?
- MAYBE I COULD COOK.
I'M PRETTY GOOD.
- REALLY?
WOW.
- I DID THE BEST I COULD WITH
WHAT I HAD. I HOPE YOU LIKE IT.
- THIS LOOKS AMAZING.
- SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK WILL?
- ABSOLUTELY DELICIOUS.
- I'M SO HAPPY YOU LIKE IT.
- HMM.
- YOU KNOW SOLTY,
IF YOU DON'T HAVE ANY PLANS
YOU'RE MORE THAN WELCOME
TO LIVE HERE WITH US.
AND IF YOU WANT TO DO ALL THE
COOKING, HEY, THAT'S FINE TOO.
- WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- THAT'S ENOUGH, WILLIAM.
- WHAT?
- DON'T BE AN IDIOT.
- WHAT'S THAT FOR?
- YOU'VE GOTTA USE YOUR HEAD.
- USE MY HEAD FOR WHAT?
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
FINE. DON'T TELL ME.
PERFECT. NOW IF YOU'LL JUST
BRING THAT PANEL OVER HERE.
- Solty: GOT IT.
- ALL RIGHT.
BRING IT IN NICE AND SLOW.
- OKAY.
- ( sighs ) I WAS WORRIED
I'D NEVER GET THIS
PUT BACK TOGETHER.
BUT SHE LOOKS AS GOOD
AS NEW, DOESN'T SHE, SOLTY?
- UH, YES.
- I COULDN'T HAVE DONE
IT WITHOUT YOU. THANKS.
- OH. SURE.
- YOU DON'T SMILE MUCH.
YOU HAVEN'T SMILED ONCE
SINCE YESTERDAY.
IS IT BECAUSE
YOU'RE UNABLE TO?
- NO, I CAN.
- YOU CALL THAT A SMILE?
THAT'S PATHETIC.
YOU KNOW, IF IT'S NONE OF MY
BUSINESS, THEN THAT'S FINE, TOO.
BUT IF YOU WANNA TALK TO SOMEONE
ABOUT IT, WELL, I'M LISTENING.
OKAY. NOW I UNDERSTAND.
SO YOU REALLY HATE
YOUR MECHANICAL BODY THAT MUCH?
- YES I DO.
BUT BECAUSE OF YOUR BODY
YOU WERE ABLE TO SAVE
YOUR FOSTER FATHER, RIGHT?
SO IT'S A GOOD THING FOR HIM
THAT YOU HAD IT.
- WELL...
- BECAUSE YOU CAN'T FEEL
ANYTHING! YOU'RE JUST A MACHINE!
- Will: AS FOR ME,
I'D DO ALMOST ANYTHING TO HAVE
A MECHANICAL BODY AT THIS POINT.
- HUH?
- ( chuckles )
PEOPLE HAVE TO DIE, RIGHT?
THEY GET HURT, OR SICK, OR MAYBE
IT'S JUST THEIR TIME TO GO.
IT'S A PART OF LIFE.
BUT WITH A MECHANICAL BODY,
YOU COULD LIVE FOREVER.
- YES, MAYBE SO, BUT ARE YOU
SURE THAT'S A GOOD THING?
- BEATS ME. I SURE WOULD LIKE
TO FIND OUT FOR MYSELF THOUGH.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS,
PEOPLE ALWAYS TEND TO
WANT WHAT THEY DON'T HAVE.
DOESN'T MATTER THAT
THEY CAN'T HAVE IT,
THEY WANT IT ANYWAY.
SAD THING IS, MOST OF THE TIME,
THE OPPOSITE IS ALSO TRUE.
BUT IF YOU'RE NOT HAPPY
WITH WHAT YOU DO HAVE,
- WELL, THE CURE FOR THAT IS
JUST TO THROW IT ALL AWAY.
- HUH?
- YOUR MECHANICAL BODY,
YOUR FOSTER FATHER, EVERYTHING.
THIS IS A PERFECT PLACE
JUST TO LET IT ALL GO.
I MEAN, IF THAT'S WHAT YOU NEED
TO DO TO FEEL BETTER.
- I DON'T THINK I CAN DO THAT.
- WHETHER IT'S FAMILY,
OR FRIENDS,
LOVE, LIFE, WHATEVER IT IS,
YOU CAN THROW IT ALL AWAY AND
START OVER ANYTIME YOU WANT.
ALL IT TAKES IS THE DECISION
TO DO IT, AND IT'S ALL GONE.
THEN AGAIN,
IF YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT REGRETS,
THEN MAYBE YOU SHOULD HOLD ON
TO EVERYTHING A LITTLE LONGER.
I MEAN, YOU'VE MADE
IT THIS FAR, RIGHT?
YOU CAN ALWAYS THROW IT
ALL AWAY LATER IF YOU WANT.
SIMPLE AS THAT.
IF IT WERE UP TO ME,
I'D WANT YOU TO STAY
HERE WITH US FOREVER.
- HUH?
- WHY'S THAT SO SURPRISING?
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS THAT
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU?
- HUH?
- ( chuckles )
- UM, I...
I'M SORRY BUT NO ONE'S EVER
SAID THAT TO ME BEFORE.
REALLY, I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT TO SAY. I, UH...
- GOTCHA.
( laughing ) I WAS ONLY KIDDING.
WOW, YOU REALLY BOUGHT IT.
I'M SORRY. IT WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE A JOKE.
GUESS I'M 0-FOR-2, HUH?
ANYWAY, LOOKS LIKE ITS
GETTING CLOSE TO SUNSET.
THINK YOU CAN COOK ANOTHER
ONE OF THOSE DELICIOUS DINNERS?
- UM, YEAH. SURE.
- GREAT. I CAN'T WAIT.
- ( vomiting )
( coughing )
DAMN. I DON'T HAVE
MUCH TIME LEFT.
- ( beeps )
- ( gasps ) MIRANDA.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- WE'VE GOT SOME INFORMATION
THAT MIGHT HELP US FIND SOLTY.
SOMEONE WHO SAYS
THEY'VE SEEN HER.
ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING
TO ME, ROY?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO DO ABOUT IT?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
- NOTHING.
- DAMMIT, ROY!
- SHE'S GONE.
RITA, TAKEN FROM ME AGAIN.
SHE'S ALL I CARED ABOUT.
SO, UNLESS YOU WANT
TO BRING RITA BACK...
( grunting )
- DON'T YOU DARE ACT LIKE YOU'RE
THE ONLY VICTIM HERE, ROY.
YOU THINK YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S LOST SOMEBODY? DO YOU?
I LOST MY HUSBAND.
YOU INSENSITIVE PRICK.
BUT I STILL HAD KASHA. I STILL
HAD A REASON TO KEEP ON LIVING.
AND YOU STILL HAD SOLTY,
YOU BASTARD!
- Solty: ROY.
- ( gasps )
- DO YOU REALLY WANT TO
LIE HERE AND DO NOTHING?
DO YOU REALLY WANT
TO LOSE HER, TOO? ANSWER ME!
- Solty: WHAT? ME TOO?
SERIOUSLY?
- Will: YEP! I WOULDN'T KID
ABOUT THAT.
AS SOON AS THE PLANE
LEAVES THE GROUND, HOP IN. OKAY?
- BUT...
- OKAY?
- OKAY.
- ( chuckles )
- ( engine starting )
- LOOKING GOOD. KEEP HER
STEADY. WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
NOW. HOP IN.
HERE WE GO!
HEY SOLTY, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
ISN'T THE VIEW AMAZING?
- YEAH. IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
- WHENEVER I GO
FLYING LIKE THIS,
IT FEELS LIKE I LEAVE
MY TROUBLES ON THE GROUND.
THE WORLD DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
SUCH A BAD PLACE FROM UP HERE.
- I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
- YOU FINALLY SMILED.
I'M ON TOP OF THE WORLD!
NOW I CAN DIE
A HAPPY MAN.
- DON'T TALK LIKE THAT.
YOU'RE TOO YOUNG TO
BE THINKING ABOUT DEATH.
YOU HAVE YOUR WHOLE LIFE
AHEAD OF YOU.
- SOLTY.
- PROMISE ME.
- C'MON, I WAS JUST KIDDING
AROUND. CAN'T YOU TAKE A JOKE?
- WILL.
- I GOTCHA. NOW, WOULD
YOU MIND LETTING GO OF ME.
GUESS THAT WASN'T FUNNY EITHER.
- WILL, ABOUT WHAT
YOU SAID YESTERDAY.
I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT IT A LOT AND WELL...
- RIGHT! ABOUT YESTERDAY,
SORRY ABOUT THAT. I REALLY
WAS JUST KIDDING AROUND.
I GUESS I JUST FELT LIKE
TEASING YOU A LITTLE BIT.
THE TRUTH IS,
I WAS FEELING JEALOUS,
MAYBE A LITTLE BIT FRUSTRATED.
I DON' T KNOW.
I JUST WANTED TO LEAVE MY OWN
LITTLE MARK ON THIS WORLD,
WHILE THERE WAS STILL TIME.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- BUT BELIEVE ME WHEN I SAY
THIS. I WAS HALF SERIOUS TOO.
- LISTEN, WILL...
WILL!
WILL, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
WILL, WAKE UP!
WILL!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( music playing )
- Solty: ROY, WHAT CAN I DO?
- Roy: TO ME, YOU ARE...
- Solty: NEXT TIME,
"HALF KIDDING."
- ♪ HANG ON TO YOUR HOPES ♪