- TWELVE YEARS AGO,
THERE WAS THIS EXPLOSION
CALLED THE BLAST FALL.
IT WAS CAUSED BY LIGHTNING
FROM THE AURORA.
MY MOM SAYS A LOT
OF PEOPLE WERE KILLED,
AND LOTS AND LOTS OF OTHERS
WERE NEVER FOUND,
SO NO ONE KNOWS WHAT
HAPPENED TO THEM.
OF COURSE,
I WASN'T EVEN BORN YET
WHEN ALL THIS IS SUPPOSED
TO HAVE HAPPENED.
( Kasha speaking )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman on TV: IN OTHER NEWS,
OFFICIALS REPORT A DRAMATIC
RISE IN INFERIN ABUSE.
ITS GROWING POPULARITY AMONG
ADOLESCENT DRUG USERS HAS LED
THE POLICE TO STEP UP
ENFORCEMENT EFFORTS,
BUT WITH LITTLE EFFECT SO FAR.
A SPOKESMAN FOR THE DEPARTMENT
NOTED THAT THE DIFFICULTY
IN IDENTIFYING THE
DRUG'S SOURCES
MAKE IT UNLIKELY
THAT THE PROBLEM
WILL BE RESOLVED ANY TIME.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING HERE?
- I HOPE YOU SLEPT WELL.
IS THAT BREAKFAST?
- DID YOU BREAK IN?
- UH, OH, NO.
IT WAS ALREADY OPEN.
- GO BACK TO MIRANDA'S PLACE.
- YOU'RE NOT A VERY GOOD COOK,
ARE YOU?
MIRANDA IS. SHE'S REALLY GOOD.
- JUST GO.
- HEY, I'LL BET YOU
DIDN'T KNOW MIRANDA
IS TEACHING ME HOW TO COOK.
- GO!
- OH, THAT GIVES ME A GREAT
IDEA, MAYBE TOMORROW...
UH...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU GOING SOMEWHERE?
- YEAH, TO WORK.
- TERRIFIC!
ALONE.
- I CAN HELP!
- NO. THAT'S NOT NECESSARY.
- BUT I WANT TO HELP YOU.
- I'M SURE YOU DO.
- OH, MY. I THINK THERE'S
SOMETHING WRONG WITH YOUR DOOR.
OH, SOLTY, I WAS WONDERING
WHERE YOU'D GOTTEN TO.
- ( giggles ) I WAS
IN ROY'S ROOM.
- MIRANDA, I WANT HIS
GIRL OUT OF THIS--
- THERE'S A LETTER
FOR YOU, SOLTY.
IT'S FROM THE CITY
WELFARE OFFICE.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT YOUR
CITIZEN STATUS.
- LET'S SEE.
"DEAR MISS SOLTY REVANT,
ACCORDING TO OUR
CURRENT RECORDS,
"YOU ARE TEMPORARILY REGISTERED
AS THE ADOPTED DAUGHTER
OF MR. ROY REVANT.
"TO COMPLETE YOUR REGISTRATION,
PLEASE BRING A COPY OF
YOUR HEALTH CERTIFICATE
"TO THE NEAREST
CITY WELFARE OFFICE.
"PLEASE COMPLY BY THE DATE
ABOVE TO AVOID A REVIEW."
HUH...
- Roy: WHAT IS THIS,
SOME KIND OF JOKE?
THE DEAL WAS YOU WERE GONNA
LOOK AFTER HER AT YOUR PLACE.
- I WAS JUST AS SURPRISED
AS YOU WERE.
I GUESS THE OFFICIAL SAW
THE TWO OF YOU TOGETHER
AND JUST ASSUMED...
FINE, YOU GOT ME.
BUT IT'S A DONE DEAL,
SO WHY NOT ACCEPT IT?
- IT'S STILL TEMPORARY.
- OH, AND YOU'RE JUST
GOING TO CANCEL IT?
- ( buzzing )
- HERE, YOUR NEXT ASSIGNMENT.
THE CLIENT JUST SO HAPPENS
TO BE A HOSPITAL,
SO YOU CAN GET
SOLTY'S PHYSICAL
TAKEN CARE OF WHILE
YOU'RE THERE.
- SAY WHAT?
- HAVE A NICE DAY, ROY.
SWEETIE, HE'LL TAKE
YOU IN JUST A MINUTE.
- HMM?
- ( sighs )
- Rose: SO, THEY GOT A HUNTER?
- Andy: YEP. LOOKS LIKE
SOMEBODY TOOK THE JOB.
- ( laughs ) I WONDER WHO THIS
LOSER IS. WHAT DOES IT SAY?
- WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
THE MORE OPPONENTS THERE ARE,
THE MORE EXCITING THE GAME IS.
- TRUE. AND LIKE EVERY
OTHER GAME WE PLAY,
WE'LL ALWAYS COME OUT ON TOP.
- ( rock song playing on radio )
- Solty: I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WE'RE GOING OUT.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME
WE'VE GONE ANYWHERE TOGETHER!
( gasps ) OH, AND
THIS HOSPITAL PLACE,
WHERE IS IT? IS IT CLOSE?
IS IT FAR?
DO THEY JUST DO PHYSICALS?
OR DO THEY DO OTHER THINGS, TOO?
IS GETTING A PHYSICAL FUN?
I'M SO EXCITED, THIS IS GREAT.
- ( turning up tempo )
- ( shouts ) WHOA, DON'T YOU
THINK THAT'S KINDA LOUD?
I CAN'T EVEN HEAR MYSELF TALK!
CAN YOU STILL HEAR ME?
ROY, CAN YOU STILL HEAR ME?
- Man over PA:
MR. CRANE. MR. CRANE.
PLEASE COME TO THE
CENTRAL PHARMACY.
YOUR PRESCRIPTION
IS NOW AVAILABLE.
- SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
THANKS FOR COMING.
YOU'LL HAVE TO EXCUSE ME,
IT'S BEEN ONE OF THOSE DAYS.
I'M NATALIE ROMAN, THE
HOSPITAL ADMINISTRATOR'S
PERSONAL SECRETARY.
YOU'RE FROM THE
HUNTERS' GUILD, RIGHT?
- YEAH. I'M ROY REVANT.
- AND I'M SOLTY REVANT.
- MMM-MMM.
- ALL RIGHTY THEN,
IF YOU'LL FOLLOW ME,
DR. BLACK IS WAITING.
( exclaims )
- UH, YOU DIDN'T HURT YOURSELF,
DID YOU?
- ( giggling )
- AS YOU MAY KNOW, THIS
HOSPITAL IS THE LARGEST GENERAL
MEDICAL COMPLEX IN THE CITY.
PEDIATRICS, OBSTETRICS,
GERIATRICS,
GENERAL AND
RECONSTRUCTIVE SURGERY.
THERE'S ALSO SPORTS MEDICINE.
PHARMACEUTICAL RESEARCH
AND DEVELOPMENT.
AND SINCE THE BLAST FALL,
WE'VE TAKEN THE LEAD IN MEETING
THE INCREASING DEMAND
FOR RESEMBLE TECHNOLOGY
AND RESEARCH, MAKING IMPORTANT
STRIDES IN CREATING MORE
SOPHISTICATED RES APPLICATIONS.
ALL RIGHTY THEN, SOLTY,
THIS NICE YOUNG ASSISTANT
WILL BE MORE THAN DELIGHTED
TO TAKE YOU TO YOUR PHYSICAL.
- I'M NOT AN ASSISTANT, I'M A
QUALIFIED RESEMBLE TECHNICIAN.
NONE OF YOU PAPER PUSHERS
GET IT RIGHT.
- WHAT?
- THAT'S ALL RIGHT, NEVER MIND.
- OKAY, THIS WAY
TO DR. BLACK'S OFFICE.
- NOT THIS WAY.
ADMINISTRATION IS THAT WAY.
- ( chuckles ) OH, THAT'S RIGHT,
SILLY ME, THIS WAY.
- ( exclaims )
- AND YOU'LL BE COMING
WITH ME, KIDDO.
YOU BETTER NOT GIVE ME
ANY TROUBLE TODAY.
- OH, RIGHT.
- ALLOW ME TO THANK YOU
FOR COMING SO QUICKLY, SIR.
IF I MAY INTRODUCE MYSELF,
I'M THE ADMINISTRATOR
OF THIS HOSPITAL.
DOCTOR DEWEY R. BLACK.
- IT'S ON YOUR NAMEPLATE.
WHAT'S THE JOB?
- ( chuckles ) SO,
THE ALL-BUSINESS TYPE.
VERY WELL,
LET'S GET DOWN TO IT THEN.
IF YOU'LL JUST FOLLOW ME.
- ( door opens )
- IT'S REALLY A VERY
SIMPLE ASSIGNMENT.
- WE WANT YOU TO MAKE
SURE THAT CASE ISN'T STOLEN.
- STOLEN?
- YES, WE RECEIVED A RATHER
BOLD, YET ANONYMOUS LETTER
BOASTING THAT IT WOULD BE TAKEN
AND THERE WAS NOTHING
WE COULD DO ABOUT IT.
- REALLY. YOU STILL HAVE IT?
- I'M VERY SORRY.
I'M AFRAID I MISPLACED IT.
- AND WHAT'S IN THIS BRIEFCASE?
- ABSOLUTELY NOTHING THAT
YOU NEED TO BE CONCERNED ABOUT.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS PROTECT
THE CASE, OR IS THAT A PROBLEM?
- ( gunshots )
- WE'VE INSTALLED A NEW
HIGH TECH SECURITY SYSTEM.
NATURALLY, I'M THE ONLY ONE
WITH THE CODE TO DISARM IT.
WE'RE MOVING THE CASE TOMORROW,
AFTER WHICH THE QUESTION
OF THEFT WILL NO
LONGER BE AN ISSUE.
- OH, AND WE'LL NEED YOU TO
PROVIDE SECURITY THEN, AS WELL.
- SO, UNLESS YOU HAVE
MORE QUESTIONS?
- NO, NO QUESTIONS.
- Solty: UM, IS THAT...
OH. IS THAT THING PART
OF THE PHYSICAL?
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO EXACTLY?
- WE'RE GOING TO PERFORM
A SCAN OF YOUR VITAL FUNCTIONS.
NOW HURRY UP AND GET
YOUR TUSH ON THE TABLE.
I HAVEN'T GOT ALL DAY,
YOU KNOW.
- OH, OKAY.
I WONDER IF ROY HAS
STARTED THE JOB ALREADY?
- ( whirring )
- I SURE WISH I WAS
HELPING HIM RIGHT NOW.
- ( gun clicks )
- SO I FIND MYSELF ASKING,
DO DOCTORS DO ELECTRICAL WORK?
( gasps ) YOU'RE JUST A KID.
- I'M NOT A KID.
- THE HELL YOU'RE NOT.
- ( gun clicks )
- Larry: ALLOW ME TO
INTRODUCE YOU.
THIS IS MY YOUNGER BROTHER,
ANDY ANDERSON.
AS FOR ME, I'M THE GUY WHO'S
GOT A GUN AIMED AT YOUR HEAD.
BUT YOU, YOU CAN CALL ME
LARRY, MR. REVANT.
- LARRY ANDERSON?
SO, YOU BOYS ARE THE
INFAMOUS ANDERSON BROTHERS?
JUDGING BY THE LETTER
YOU SENT IN ADVANCE,
I GUESS YOU'RE AS ARROGANT
AS THEY SAY YOU ARE.
- YOU'VE GOT A BIT
OF A REP YOURSELF.
I HEARD YOU REALLY
TORE UP THE UNDERWORLD.
OF COURSE THAT
WAS A WHILE BACK,
WHEN YOU WERE LOOKING
FOR YOUR MISSING KID.
EASY. I DON'T WANT
ANY EXTRA WORK.
JUST DON'T MOVE.
- WHAT'RE YOU GUYS
PLANNING TO DO?
- THAT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
JUST SIT BACK
AND ENJOY THE SHOW.
- SCANNING SYSTEMS.
OPERATING NORMALLY.
EVERYTHING CHECKS OUT. SO...
HUH?
- ( electronic beeping )
- ( gasps ) WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
BUT THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
- ( beeping )
- I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
I'VE GOT TO GET MORE
POWER TO THE SCANNER.
I'VE GOT TO RUN MORE TESTS.
CHECK HER REACTIONS.
- WAIT! YOU ASSHOLES AREN'T
GOING TO CUT THE POWER, ARE YOU?
ARE YOU COMPLETELY INSANE?
THERE MUST BE DOZENS
OF PEOPLE ON LIFE SUPPORT
OR IN SURGERY RIGHT NOW,
- THEY COULD ALL BE KILLED.
- SHUT YOUR FACE, GRANDPA!
- THE BACKUP
GENERATORS WILL KICK IN
RIGHT AFTER WE PULL THE PLUG.
SOON AS IT DOES, WE'LL STRIKE.
IT'LL BE OVER IN A MOMENT.
NOTHING WILL HAPPEN
TO THE PATIENTS.
IT'S A SIMPLE GAME.
- EXCUSE ME, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- Yuto: RELAX, THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
THE SENSOR PADS ARE FOR
A COUPLE MORE LITTLE TESTS.
JUST A SEC.
HERE WE GO. EASY.
- ( explosion )
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- HUH?
- THAT'S ODD.
( exclaims )
- ANDY, NO!
- THAT WASN'T ME.
- ( grunting )
- LARRY!
- ( gunshot )
- ( groans )
DAMN.
- THIS IS UNACCEPTABLE, SIR.
YOU ALLOWED THOSE FELONS
TO ESCAPE FROM UNDER
YOUR VERY NOSE.
- PARDON ME, DOCTOR.
BUT HE DID STOP THEM
FROM STEALING THE CASE.
WHO ASKED YOU!
GROSS INCOMPETENCE.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
THERE'S NO OTHER WAY
TO DESCRIBE IT.
I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT
TO ADD EXTRA HUNTERS
TO THE GUARD DETAIL
FOR TOMORROW'S TRANSPORT.
AND, SIR, THE MONEY
FOR THOSE HUNTERS
WILL COME OUT OF
YOUR REMUNERATION.
IS THAT PERFECTLY CLEAR?
- YEAH, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
- Man: OKAY, LISTEN.
I KNOW YOU WANNA BE A BIG SHOT
RESEMBLE TECHNICIAN SOMEDAY,
BUT UNTIL THEN,
YOU REALLY CAN'T GO AROUND
TAPPING INTO THE MAIN POWER
GRID WITHOUT AUTHORIZATION.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU
BLOW EVERYTHING UP
AND BLACK OUT THE HOSPITAL
IN THE PROCESS.
- AWESOME. AWESOME.
- WHAT?
- THAT GIRL WAS REALLY AWESOME!
IF I COULD JUST EXAMINE
HER AGAIN, I COULD...
AWESOME. SHE WAS SO AWESOME.
- YOU ARE SO FIRED.
- UH, ARE YOU...
- GET SOME SLEEP.
- OKAY.
GOOD NIGHT.
THERE SURE ARE A LOT
OF PEOPLE HERE, ROY.
- AH, JUST IGNORE 'EM.
ALL THAT MATTERS THAT WE
CONCENTRATE ON DOING OUR JOB.
- OKAY.
- EXCELLENT, GENTLEMEN,
LET'S MOVE OUT.
( chuckles ) WITH THIS KIND OF
SECURITY, THOSE MISCREANTS
WILL HAVE TO THINK TWICE
BEFORE THEY TRY ANYTHING.
- UH, ROY, IS IT A GOOD IDEA
TO BE SO FAR BACK?
- HA! I TOLD YOU THIS
WAS GONNA BE SIMPLE.
- YEAH, LOOKS LIKE IT'S GONNA
BE EASY MONEY TODAY, BOYS.
- ( car tires squealing )
- ( gasps )
- SORRY WE'RE LATE. LET'S BEGIN.
- OKAY, TAKE 'EM DOWN.
- WHAT THE HELL?
( gasps )
- ( gasps ) WHAT HAPPENED?
- HANG ON TIGHT!
- Man: HEY, HEY KENT,
SLOW DOWN.
I THINK SOMETHING'S
GOING DOWN BEHIND THE TRANSPORT.
- Andy: YOU DON'T MISS A THING,
DO YOU?
AFRAID YOUR BUDDIES
ARE OUT OF THE GAME.
- OH, YOU BASTARD!
- ( bell ringing )
- HEY, LOOK.
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
- WHERE?
- Kasha: I TOTALLY GOT AN A.
- YOU'RE KIDDING.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- WHOA, MAN. THAT SUCKS.
- ( explosion )
- Andy: HEY LARRY, THIS GUY
DOESN'T KNOW WHEN TO QUIT.
- Larry: BUT YOU GOTTA
ADMIRE HIS DEDICATION.
- OKAY, THEN WE'LL HAVE
TO DO THE OL' SMASH N' GRAB.
( laughs ) THIS IS MORE
MY STYLE, ANYWAY.
OH YEAH, COME TO DADDY.
- ( gunshot )
- WHAT THE...
- THAT WAS FOR YESTERDAY.
- I WANNA HELP, TOO!
- WAIT. SOLTY.
- GIMME THAT CASE, YOU LITTLE...
- ( sighs ) THEY'RE SO
FAR AHEAD OF US NOW,
WE MAY NEVER CATCH UP.
- SPARE ME THE TRAFFIC
REPORT, MISSY.
GET THIS CAR MOVING BEFORE
THOSE CROOKS CAN GET AWAY.
- YOU KNOW, DEWEY,
I DON'T KNOW HOW THE REAL
NATALIE PUTS UP WITH YOU.
- THE REAL NATALIE,
WHAT DO YOU...
( gasps )
- YEAH, THE ONE
WHO'S BEEN RESTING
COMFORTABLY AT HOME
SINCE YESTERDAY.
( giggles )
SEE YA!
- FOR THE LOVE OF...
JUST HOLD STILL!
- ( screaming )
( chuckles ) LOOK, I GOT IT.
HEY, ROY!
- THAT A GIRL.
- ( whizzing )
- ( gasps )
- WE LIVE IN SAD, SAD TIMES.
FOOLS AND VILLAINS
RULE THE WORLD,
AND THE PEOPLE DESPAIR.
BUT NOW A METEOR FALLS
FROM THE HEAVENS
LIKE A RAY OF HOPE,
LIGHTING UP THIS DARK
-WORLD LIKE A BEACON.
- Roy: WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- OPPRESSORS BE WARNED!
ROSE, THE BRIGHT BLUE METEOR
OF HOPE IS HERE.
- I DOUBT HER PARENTS
WOULD APPROVE OF THIS.
- ROSE, YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO BE BACKUP.
- A GOOD OFFENSE IS
THE BEST DEFENSE.
- WHAT THE HELL'S
THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- QUIT GRANDSTANDING.
- OH, SHUT UP!
- WE GOT THE THINGY, DIDN'T WE?
NOW LET'S GO, SO I CAN SHOWER.
- Solty: WAIT A MINUTE.
- HMM?
- YOU GIVE THAT
CASE BACK RIGHT NOW.
- ( exclaims )
- Dewey: WAIT, THE CONTENTS
OF THAT CASE ARE FRAGILE.
- SHUT UP! I'M NOT GONNA LET
THOSE TWO-BIT HOODS GET AWAY.
- Dewey: ( shouts ) NO!
- ( screams )
- LOOK OUT ROY!
- ARE YOU CRAZY? STOP!
- ( yelling )
- WHOA!
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- YES. I'M GLAD TO SEE
THAT YOU'RE OKAY, TOO.
- LOOK, SOLTY...
- Larry: YO, REVANT!
- UH, ROY, LOOK!
- ROSE!
- OKAY! CANNON MODE ACTIVATE.
FIRE!
- THIS IS...
- Larry: BINGO. IT'S INFERIN.
WE WERE OUT TO EXPOSE
DR. BLACK FROM THE START.
- YEAH, THAT SCUMBAG'S BEEN
STEALING IT FROM THE HOSPITAL
AND SELLING IT
TO KIDS ON THE STREET.
NOW I WANNA KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GONNA DO ABOUT THE DAMAGE...
- HUH, MODERN ROBIN HOODS.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU KNOW.
- HEY, ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
- LET'S GO.
- SOLTY!
- HUH?
- I REALLY ENJOYED OUR
LITTLE GAME TODAY.
AND GIRL, I GOT TO ADMIT
YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD. TA-TA!
WE'LL MEET AGAIN.
- BYE.
- MY CASE.
( groans ) DESTROYED.
- TRAFFICKING INFERIN.
IS THAT IT, DOC?
- YEAH, NO, NO.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
- A HOSPITAL ADMINISTRATOR
DABBLING IN NARCOTICS.
- SOUNDS LIKE A HUGE
SCANDAL TO ME.
( scoffs ) LET'S SEE YOU TALK
YOUR WAY OUT OF THIS ONE.
- Kasha: GREAT. THE CLIENT GETS
ARRESTED SO WE DON'T GET PAID.
WHAT A RIP.
ALL THAT HARD WORK FOR NOTHING.
- IS IT POSSIBLE TO MAKE
MONEY DOING NOTHING?
- UH, NO.
- Roy: THERE'S YOUR
NEW I.D. CARD.
- HMM?
- I HAD TO GO BY THE
CENTER ANYWAY, SO...
- UM, THANKS.
- WHY WOULD YOU HAVE
TO GO BY THE CENTER?
- I...
- OH, GOOD.
I'M GLAD EVERYBODY'S HERE.
GUYS, THERE'S SOMEONE
I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET.
HE'S MOVING INTO
THE APARTMENT NEXT DOOR.
SAY HELLO TO YUTO K. STEEL.
HE'S GOING TO BE TAKING OVER AS
OUR NEW MAINTENANCE TECHNICIAN
AND ELECTRONICS EXPERT.
UH, YUTO?
- OH, TO BE NEAR
YOU AGAIN. AT LONG LAST.
OH, YOUR HANDS ARE SO SOFT
AND SUPPLE, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I WANT TO EXAMINE ALL OF YOU.
I'LL PAY YOU FOR YOUR TIME...
- WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR?
- HE'S A FREAKING PERVERT.
CALL THE COPS.
- JUST A MINUTE,
WHO ARE YOU CALLING A PERVERT?
I'M A HIGHLY TRAINED
RESEMBLE TECHNICIAN.
- Roy: YOU'RE A HIGHLY
TRAINED PERVERT.
- Yuto: MIRANDA! HELP!
- Roy: THEY JUST LOVE
GUYS LIKE YOU IN PRISON!
- "SOLTY REVANT."
- Yuto: I'M SORRY! I'M SORRY!
- Roy: OH, I'LL TELL YOU
WHEN YOU'RE SORRY!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Solty: SUCH A NICE
LITTLE GIRL.
MY VERY FIRST FRIEND.
DO YOU HAVE ONE?