- Rose: IN THE CITY,
THE PEOPLE ARE DIVIDED IN TWO
AS SURELY AS IF THERE IS
A WALL BETWEEN THEM.
EXCEPT THE WALL, IN THIS CASE,
IS A SIMPLE PIECE OF PLASTIC,
A CITIZEN I.D. CARD.
REGISTERED CARD-HOLDERS
ARE CALLED COMPENTERS,
UNREGISTERED CITIZENS,
INCOMPENTERS.
REGISTERED CITIZENS ARE
GUARANTEED A LIVING,
HEALTH CARE AND EDUCATION.
AND MANY OTHER CITY SERVICES.
IT'S THEIR RIGHT.
THE UNREGISTERED CITIZENS
HAVE NO SUCH RIGHTS.
THEY HAVE NO GUARANTEES.
THIS LITTLE PIECE OF PLASTIC
IS GREATER THAN ANY WALL.
ON ONE SIDE ARE THE
PRIVILEGED, THE COMPENTERS.
ON THE OTHER SIDE, THE
INCOMPENTERS, THE OPPRESSED.
WELL, I DON'T REALLY CARE
ABOUT SUCH THINGS.
- ( gasps )
- ( alarm sounding )
- ( gasping )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Roy: SO WHO'S THIS?
- Miranda: HE'S THE PERP IN
THE P 10 CRYSTAL ROBBERY
TWO DAYS AGO.
TWO GUARDS WERE SHOT.
- OH, MURDER THEN?
- NO, THE HOSPITAL SAYS THE
GUARDS ARE GOING TO MAKE IT,
BUT IT WAS A PRETTY CLOSE CALL.
- AN UNREGISTERED CITIZEN.
HE'S NOT GONNA BE
AN EASY ONE TO FIND.
- I'VE NEVER HEARD OF THIS
P 10 STUFF HE STOLE,
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
- OH, IT'S...
- Yuto: A RARE
CRYSTALLINE COMPOUND.
- HUH?
ITS UNIQUENESS LIES IN
ITS GREATER CLARITY
AND HIGHER REFRACTION INDEX
THAN MOST ORDINARY CRYSTALS.
WHAT'S MORE, IT HAS
OPTO-ELECTRIC PROPERTIES
THAT GIVE IT AN INCREDIBLE
RANGE OF HIGH-TECH APPLICATIONS.
IT'S ONE OF THE HOTTEST
NEW MATERIALS OUT THERE.
A HANDFUL OF THE PURE STUFF
IS NEARLY PRICELESS.
HOWEVER, REFINING PURE
GRADE P 10 CRYSTAL
IS A PRETTY TRICKY PROCESS, SO
IT'S STILL IN SHORT SUPPLY.
- IS THAT SO? 'CAUSE
THE REPORT SAYS
HE GOT AWAY WITH A
PILE OF THE STUFF.
- THEN IT MUST'VE BEEN
A LOWER GRADE OF CRYSTAL.
IT WOULD STILL HAVE A
PRETTY HIGH STREET VALUE,
BUT IMPURE P 10 IS
EXTREMELY UNSTABLE.
IT HAS TO BE HANDLED
VERY CAREFULLY OR ELSE KABOOM.
- WELL, ROY,
YOU WANT THE JOB?
- "KABOOM"?
- I GUESS SO.
- ( phone ringing )
- HEY, ROY. PHONE CALL.
YOU CAN TAKE IT IN
THERE IF YOU WANT.
- PUT ME ON IT, MIRANDA.
THIS IS ROY.
- OKAY. I'LL START UP
THE PAPERWORK.
- KABOOM.
- WHAT? YOU'VE GOT TO
BE KIDDING ME.
I'M LEAVING.
- WAIT UP.
- HEY.
- ARE WE ON THE JOB NOW?
HUH, ROY?
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- SO WHAT WAS THAT MYSTERIOUS
PHONE CALL ALL ABOUT?
I BET YOU ALREADY GOT
A LEAD ON THE PERP
AND WE'RE HOT ON
HIS TRAIL, AM I RIGHT?
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- COME ON, YOU CAN TELL US.
YOU GOTTA KEEP US IN THE LOOP
OR WE'RE NOT GONNA...
- SHUT UP, DAMN IT!
MY DAUGHTER,
SHE'S BEEN FOUND.
- YOUR DAUGHTER?
- ( giggling )
DADDY?
- THEY DON'T LEARN.
- ( scoffs )
- WHERE'S RITA?
YOU SON-OF-A...
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS
OF SEARCHING...
- ( car doors closing )
- Yuto: IS THIS THE ONE?
- YEAH. I THINK SO.
- THIS IS WONDERFUL. YOU'VE
FOUND HER AFTER ALL THIS TIME.
- UH.
HMM.
- Yuto: HEY, SOLTY, YOU COMING?
- UH, YEAH.
- YES?
- I'M LOOKING FOR
A RITA REVANT.
I WAS TOLD THIS
MIGHT BE HER HOUSE.
- I'M RITA REVANT.
- ( gasps )
- MAY I ASK YOUR NAME, PLEASE?
- I'M... MY NAME IS ROY REVANT.
- HANG ON. IT'LL TAKE ME
A MOMENT TO OPEN THE DOOR.
- ( gasping )
- WHAT DO YOU
THINK, IS IT HER?
- WELL, ROY?
- SHE... SHE'S NOT THE ONE.
- I SEE.
SO YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR YOUR DAUGHTER.
- UH, YEAH.
- REVANT ISN'T ACTUALLY MY
LAST NAME. IT'S THE ONE THE
CITY REGISTRATION OFFICE
GAVE ME TWELVE YEARS AGO.
I LOST MY EYESIGHT AND THE USE
OF MY LEGS IN THE BLAST FALL.
I WAS FIVE YEARS
OLD AT THE TIME.
I REMEMBERED MY FIRST NAME
WAS RITA. BUT I COULDN'T RECALL
ANYTHING ELSE
ABOUT MY OLD LIFE.
SO I ENDED UP BECOMING
A WARD OF THE CITY.
- SO YOU'RE A NEW RIGHTS CHILD?
- NEW RIGHTS? WHAT'S THAT?
- AFTER THE BLAST FALL,
UNIDENTIFIED CHILDREN WERE
MADE WARDS OF THE CITY.
A SPECIAL LAW WAS PASSED,
SO THEY COULD REGISTER
AND BECOME FULL CITIZENS.
ANY CHILD WHO QUALIFIED
CAME TO BE KNOWN AS
A NEW RIGHTS CHILD.
- YES, I WAS ONE OF
THOSE CHILDREN.
IF IT WASN'T FOR THE LAW AND
THE SPECIAL ALLOWANCE I GET,
IT WOULDN'T BE POSSIBLE FOR ME
TO LIVE HERE ON MY OWN.
- I KNOW.
- I'M... I'M SORRY.
- OH, YOU DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO APOLOGIZE FOR.
- ( car approaching )
- UNCLE IS HERE.
- Yuto: UNCLE? BUT...
- WELL, HE'S... I CALL HIM
UNCLE BECAUSE HE'S SO KIND.
HE SAYS MY FATHER HELPED
HIM ONCE A LONG TIME AGO.
- ( sighs )
- ( door opening )
- HELLO, RITA.
- COME IN. I WANT YOU
TO MEET MY GUESTS.
- GUESTS?
COME ON.
- HUH?
- ( exclaiming )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER...
- RITA!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, HONEY?
- I'M SORRY.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE A VERY STRONG GIRL.
- OH, NO.
- IT MUST BE NICE. I WISH
I WAS AS STRONG AS YOU.
- OH, WELL... OH!
- UH, DO YOU...
- WHAT?
- DO YOU REALLY LIVE HERE
ALL BY YOURSELF?
- YES, I DO.
- BUT ISN'T THAT
KIND OF DIFFICULT?
- I DON'T MIND.
- UH?
- I'VE ALWAYS GOT UNCLE.
I OWE HIM EVERYTHING.
HE'S LOOKED AFTER ME
EVER SINCE THE BLAST FALL.
I CAN'T BEGIN TO TELL YOU ALL
THE THINGS HE'S DONE FOR ME.
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO
THANK HIM ENOUGH.
HE'S ALWAYS THERE FOR ME.
HE'S THE ONLY REAL
FAMILY I'VE EVER KNOWN.
- OKAY, WHAT'S
GOING ON? VINCENT.
LISTEN TO ME, THIS MORNING I
GOT A BOUNTY WARRANT
FOR YOUR CAPTURE, RIGHT?
THEN YOU JUST
SHOW UP HERE?
HOW DO YOU KNOW
THAT GIRL IN THERE?
- RITA IS MY DAUGHTER.
- BULLSHIT!
DON'T YOU GIVE ME THAT.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE HER FATHER?
THEN WHY DON'T
YOU TELL HER THAT?
- BECAUSE I'M AN
UNREGISTERED CITIZEN.
IF THE CITY FINDS OUT RITA'S
FATHER IS UNREGISTERED,
SHE'LL LOSE HER NEW RIGHTS
STATUS, ALL HER BENEFITS.
I CAN'T SAY ANYTHING
AND YOU KNOW IT.
- AND I SUPPOSE THAT JUSTIFIES
SHOOTING TWO PEOPLE?
- I DID IT SO SHE COULD
SEE AND WALK AGAIN.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
A RESEMBLE EYE COSTS?
A RESEMBLE LEG?
AN AVERAGE GUY LIKE ME COULD
WORK FOR THREE LIFETIMES,
AND STILL NOT HAVE THE
CASH FOR THE OPERATIONS.
- IS THAT WHY YOU
TOOK THE P10?
- RITA'S BEEN SITTING IN TOTAL
DARKNESS FOR TWELVE YEARS.
IF THERE'S A CHANCE FOR HER
TO WALK IN THE LIGHT AGAIN,
I WOULD DO ANYTHING
TO MAKE IT HAPPEN.
ANYTHING, YOU HEAR? ANYTHING!
- ROY, NO.
- HOLD IT!
- Solty: ROY?
- WHAT?
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
WILL YOU ARREST VINCENT?
WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO RITA?
- Kelly: FOR GOD SAKE, VINCENT,
JUST CHILL OUT, WILL YOU?
- BUT KELLY, THEY SENT
A HUNTER AFTER ME!
- HEY, RELAX.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- DON'T WORRY? I GOT
CAUGHT BY A SECURITY CAMERA.
YOU TOLD ME THEY DIDN'T
HAVE ELECTRONIC SURVEILLANCE.
- THEY DIDN'T WHEN I LOOKED
THE PLACE OVER.
I WAS JUST AS
SURPRISED AS YOU.
VINCENT, I SCREWED UP,
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
- OKAY.
- YOU JUST GOTTA STAY COOL.
I'VE MADE ALL THE ARRANGEMENTS
FOR RITA'S OPERATION.
YOU ONLY NEED A
LITTLE MORE CASH.
WE'RE GOOD TO GO
ON YOUR NEXT HEIST.
SO IT'S UP TO YOU, MY MAN,
ARE YOU IN OR ARE YOU OUT?
- OKAY, BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE HUNTER?
- JUST LEAVE HIM TO ME.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL ME
KELLY JONES, THE FIXER.
- RITA, IT WON'T BE LONG NOW,
AND YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
SEE AGAIN, AND WALK.
I'LL DISAPPEAR,
SO YOU CAN START A NEW LIFE.
IT'LL BE BETTER IF I'M GONE.
YOU WOULDN'T WANT PEOPLE TO
KNOW THAT YOUR FATHER'S A CROOK.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
YOU'RE STRONG, LIKE YOUR MOTHER.
ONCE YOUR EYES AND
LEGS ARE REPAIRED,
YOU WON'T NEED ME ANYMORE.
THIS'LL BE THE
LAST JOB I PULL.
- Solty: MR. VINCENT?
- ( gasping )
- ( chuckles )
FOR ONCE, CAN'T YOU
LET SOMEONE GO?
- DARN, THAT KID.
- ( knocking on door )
- YEAH?
- I GOT THE DNA ANALYSIS
YOU WANTED.
THERE'S NO QUESTION ABOUT IT,
VINCENT IS DEFINITELY
RITA'S FATHER.
- ( sighing )
- ( phone ringing )
- YEAH. IT'S ME.
- IT'S MIRANDA. I RAN THE
CHECKS YOU ASKED FOR.
- OKAY, LET'S HEAR IT.
- VINCENT GRECO. I FOUND
ONLY ONE PRIOR ON HIM.
A STRETCH FOR
LARCENY YEARS AGO.
BUT UP UNTIL THIS
P 10 BUSINESS,
IT LOOKED LIKE HE WAS
KEEPING HIMSELF CLEAN.
IT SAYS HE WAS MARRIED,
WITH ONE CHILD, A DAUGHTER.
HIS WIFE WAS KILLED
IN THE BLAST FALL.
HIS DAUGHTER IS
LISTED AS MISSING.
ACCORDING TO THE
BIRTH CERTIFICATE,
THE DAUGHTER'S NAME WAS...
- RITA.
- THIS IS TURNING
INTO QUITE A MESS.
- SORRY.
- NOT YOUR FAULT.
BUT WATCH YOURSELF.
GRECO'S GOT SOME SHADY
CHARACTERS BACKING HIM UP...
- WHAT? MIRANDA, ARE YOU...
- IS SHE OKAY?
- GET DOWN!
- ( gun firing )
- ( footsteps approaching )
- Vincent: ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS?
- Solty: YES. I'M GONNA
HELP YOU.
BECAUSE RITA IS DEPENDING ON US.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- Roy: STOP RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE.
OKAY, GRECO, HANDS ON YOUR HEAD
AND KNEEL DOWN ON THE FLOOR.
- BUT, ROY...
- SOLTY, JUST SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
ARE YOU NUTS? ARE YOU TRYING
TO BE A CRIMINAL, TOO?
VINCENT GRECO, A BOUNTY HAS
BEEN ISSUED FOR YOUR ARREST
FOR THE THEFT OF
THE P 10 CRYSTALS
AND THE ASSAULT OF TWO
SECURITY OFFICERS.
IF YOU RESIST, I...
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
YOU STOPPED US, SO WHY CAN'T
YOU JUST LET HIM GO?
YOU KNOW HE'S ONLY DOING
THIS SO HE CAN HELP RITA.
- YUTO'S BEEN SHOT!
- ( gasps )
- HE'S NOT DEAD,
BUT HE'S IN INTENSIVE CARE
THANKS TO GRECO'S BUDDIES.
YOU STILL THINK
THIS IS A GOOD IDEA?
IF RITA KNEW THAT THE
MONEY FOR HER TREATMENT
CAME FROM ROBBERY
AND ATTEMPTED MURDER,
HOW DO YOU THINK IT
WOULD MAKE HER FEEL?
DO YOU THINK SHE'D WANT THIS?
YOU'VE GOT ALL THE ANSWERS,
YOU RIGHTEOUS PRICK.
BUT YOU WEREN'T SO UPRIGHT
WHEN YOU WERE LOOKING
FOR YOUR DAUGHTER.
- CAN'T YOU UNDERSTAND
THAT I HAVE TO DO THIS?
- DON'T BE A SAP, GRECO.
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK
THIS IS THE BEST WAY
TO HELP YOUR DAUGHTER?
- IT IS. IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
I'D GIVE MY LIFE FOR HER
IF THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES.
- ( gunshot )
- VINCENT, NO!
- ( clapping ) BRAVO. BRAVO.
NOW THAT IS TRULY WHAT I CALL
AN AWARD-WINNING PERFORMANCE.
VINCENT, IT'S TIME TO
LOWER THE CURTAIN.
- ( groaning ) KELLY?
- ( laughs )
- NOT A GOOD IDEA.
- ( footsteps pattering )
- GUYS, I'D LIKE TO
INTRODUCE YOU TO
A COUPLE OF MY FRIENDS.
- Vincent: WHY DID YOU
TURN ON ME?
- ( scoffs ) TURN ON YOU?
NO, NO, NO.
THIS WAS MY PLAN FROM
THE VERY BEGINNING.
I'M SICK OF LIVING WITH THE
VERMIN IN THE
SHADOWS OF SOCIETY.
I'M GETTING WAY TOO
OLD FOR ALL THE
BLOODSHED AND BULLETS.
SO, NOW I'M GONNA BUY
MYSELF A FULL CITIZENSHIP
AND A COMFORTABLE RETIREMENT,
AND YOU'VE MADE IT
ALL POSSIBLE.
THANKS, OF COURSE,
TO YOUR GENEROUS CONTRIBUTION.
P 10 CRYSTAL.
SURE, IT MAY BE LOW GRADE,
BUT IT'S STILL WORTH PLENTY
TO THE RIGHT PEOPLE.
AND AS A BONUS,
IT DOES THIS!
- ( explosion )
- GETS ME EVERY TIME.
- BUT RITA... WHAT ABOUT
HER RESEMBLE SURGERY,
YOU PROMISED...
- I LIED. SO SUE ME.
- ( coughing )
STOP IT!
- OOPS. ALMOST FORGOT
ABOUT YOU TWO.
BUT DON'T WORRY,
WE ALL GET TO PLAY A PART.
YOU SEE, THERE'S VINCENT,
DESPERATE FUGITIVE WITH
A PRICE ON HIS HEAD,
HE TRIES TO ROB
A BANK, THEN YOU,
THE SAD, DISGRUNTLED
BOUNTY HUNTER,
YOU TRACK HIM DOWN,
AND AFTER A FIERCE FIGHT
YOU BOTH GET BLOWN TO BITS
IN A P 10 CRYSTAL EXPLOSION.
AND THE STOLEN MONEY IS
BURNED TO ASHES IN THE DISASTER.
WELL, ACTUALLY IT GOES
INTO MY POCKETS,
BUT NO ONE WILL EVER KNOW THAT.
PRETTY CONVINCING
SCENARIO, ISN'T IT?
- Solty: YOU ROTTEN CREEP.
YOU TOOK ADVANTAGE OF VINCENT,
YOU'LL BE SORRY.
I'LL MAKE YOU SORRY.
- ( gasps )
SHOOT HER. SHOOT HER!
- ( guns firing )
- HEY. HEY.
- I DID...
- DON'T TALK.
SAVE YOUR STRENGTH.
- I DID IT FOR RITA, I...
- I KNOW, I KNOW.
JUST KEEP STILL.
- I MANAGED TO GET THIS.
- ( gasps )
- USE IT TO FIX RITA'S EYES.
USE IT...
- I'LL DO WHAT I CAN.
- WELL ROY, I GUESS I WASN'T
VERY MUCH OF A FATHER, WAS I?
( gasps )
- NO, VINCENT, YOU CAN'T DIE.
C'MON, NOT NOW. YOU GOT TO LIVE,
YOUR DAUGHTER NEEDS YOU.
- ( grunting )
WELL, DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
FINISH HER OFF.
SHOOT HER. KILL HER.
- I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN.
- ( firing )
- THE BULLETS JUST BOUNCE
RIGHT OFF OF HER.
- HOW COULD YOU?
( yelling )
- ( exclaiming in fear )
- SOLTY, YOU OKAY?
- ROY, WHERE'S VINCENT?
- NOW'S OUR CHANCE,
EXTERMINATE THEM.
- DAMN IT.
THERE'S JUST TOO MANY.
- VINCENT. VINCENT.
- SORRY, MAN.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO BORROW THIS.
ASSUMING WE GET
OUT OF HERE ALIVE,
I PROMISE I'LL PAY YOU BACK.
- ( all screaming )
- ( groaning )
- WELL, THAT'S THAT.
- YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
PLEASE, VINCENT.
YOU CAN'T DIE. YOU CAN'T.
RITA SAID YOU'RE ALWAYS
THERE FOR HER.
RITA SAID YOU WERE HER FAMILY.
YOU CAN'T JUST LEAVE
HER LIKE THIS.
VINCENT...
PLEASE, YOU CAN'T
DIE LIKE THIS.
- OH. HE SAID THAT?
- UH, YEAH. HE SAID HE HAD
TO GO AWAY FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- I UNDERSTAND.
- BUT HE LEFT ME WITH THE MONEY
TO PAY FOR YOUR SURGERY.
A COMPLETE RESEMBLE TREATMENT
FOR YOUR EYES AND LEGS.
IF AND WHEN YOU DECIDE
TO HAVE THE SURGERY,
I'LL BE GLAD TO HELP YOU OUT.
CENTRAL'LL PROBABLY SEND SOMEONE
OUT HERE DAY AFTER TOMORROW,
MAYBE EVEN SOONER.
SO, UH...
- TELL ME, PLEASE.
WHERE IS HE? WHERE'S HE NOW?
- I DON'T KNOW. HE DIDN'T
SAY WHERE HE WAS GOING.
- OH, I SEE.
MAY I ASK A FAVOR?
IF YOU SHOULD TALK TO HIM, WOULD
YOU TELL HIM I SAID THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
AND THAT I'LL DO IT.
- YEAH, SURE.
- ONE MORE THING.
PLEASE TELL HIM THAT
I'LL BE WAITING FOR HIM,
NO MATTER HOW LONG HE'S GONE.
TELL MY DAD THAT FOR ME.
- BUT... OF COURSE.
I'LL TELL HIM.
- ( sighs )
- ARE YOU SURE YOU
DON'T WANNA SEE HER?
- NO, I CAN'T.
- WELL ANYWAY,
I USED YOUR BOUNTY TO PAY
YOU BACK FOR THE CRYSTAL.
AND THE BOUNTY ON
KELLY AND HIS GANG
SHOULD LEAVE YOU
WITH SOME CHANGE.
LET'S GO.
- I LOVE YOU, SOLTY.
- UH...
ROSE?
- HEY, WELCOME BACK, GUYS.
I'VE GOT SOME GOOD NEWS.
I'M GONNA BE MOVING IN
FOR A WHILE. OKEY-DOKEY?
- UH?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Rose: WHY IS THIS ROOM
SUCH A MESS?
- Solty: UM, ACTUALLY
I JUST CLEANED IT.
NEXT TIME, "A LITTLE
DEMON COMES TO VISIT."
- Rose: I THINK I'M GONNA
TAKE YOUR ROOM.
- Solty: OH!