[gunshot]
Is there ever a moment's
peace around here?
[KATSUIE] Nobunaga‐sama
brought in a musket specialist.
Sounds like they're doing
some test shooting.
Hm? What do you
mean brought in?
He's from Sakai.
Goes by the name
Takigawa Kazumasu.
Wow!
Well done!
Beautiful shot, Kichou‐sama.
If so, it's only because I have
such an excellent instructor.
[NOBUNAGA]
There's more to it.
These models are lighter and
more powerful than the old ones.
Even women and children
will be able to wield these.
You aren't serious.
Sure.
The battlefield
is going to change.
Good work, Takigawa‐dono.
Keep improving on the design.
I shall, my lord.
[KICHOU] The weight's
a definite improvement,
and it would allow more people
to learn how to shoot a musket.
But the problem is with speed.
It still takes too
much time to reload.
I've got a workaround
and when you see it,
you're going to be amazed
at how simple it is.
[chuckles]
Did I say something funny?
It's just that I've never seen
this level of excitement
in you before.
Well, I suppose sometimes
when I'm around people who're
close to me, I get carried away.
Just goes to show, you're
a part of our family, now.
[laughs]
[KICHOU]
Oda Nobunaga.
When the world was at war,
he eclipsed it like a demon god.
Though much has
been written about him,
the man I knew
differed from the legend.
Tonight, let me tell you
a bit more about who that
Nobunaga‐sama really was.
Five hundred?
Surely I didn't hear
you right, my lord!
There are a 100 from Sakai,
and a further 150 from
the Kunitomo smithy,
but I figure we still need
around double that number.
Can we arrange for that somehow?
One moment, my lord.
I remain confused
regarding this request.
Why would we ever need
that many muskets?
Obviously to defend Owari.
Surely you jest, my lord!
Muskets are used as
nothing more than a ploy
to startle the enemy forces!
Five Hundred.
While it's true that only
one won't do much more
than scare away
a flock of sparrows.
Imagine if we had 500.
We'd be able to drive away
even the Imagawa.
But our bows are sufficient!
If you know where to
locate 500 master archers,
I'm all ears, Katsuie
How do you expect
to pay for this?
As my retainers,
it's your responsibility to
figure out the how, not mine.
This is pure nonsense.
I never imagined he'd
be this unreasonable.
[HIRATE] Leave the details
for me to sort through, my lord.
I, Hirate Masahide,
your loyal servant,
shall arrange for the
remaining 250 muskets.
Lord Auditor!
Do you think it's advisable?
Making such rash assurances?
A senior retainer's job is
to carry out his orders.
If the role simply involved
voicing displeasure,
an infant would
make a better choice.
Well, my lord?
It's settled.
I assign the task
to you, Hirate.
It would be my honor.
Why, Brother?
Why do you continue
to allow that old sycophant
to give into the
brat's every whim?
At this point, Hirate‐dono
is the lord's only supporter!
We should oust him and force
Nobukatsu‐sama into power!
But instead, we continue
letting his foolish brother
destroy the Oda clan!
You should choose
your words more carefully.
None of us can hold
a candle to his legacy.
Surely even
you're aware of that.
When Hirate‐dono was younger,
he tore across the battlefield
as Nobuhide‐sama's
right‐hand man.
Enemies could never get near
him thanks to the masterful way
he wielded a spear.
Outside of battle,
it was much the same.
No one outdid him in
governmental affairs.
In fact, all negotiations with
the Imperial Court came
to fruition because
of his diplomatic skills.
Now that I think back,
there was one incident.
A foreign ship had been caught
in a storm and shipwrecked.
So, Hirate‐dono
set off on his own.
They say he rescued
every crew member.
[HIDESADA] The barbarians
he saved were so grateful.
Every one of them went
so far as to make a promise.
Should Hirate‐dono
ever require their help,
no matter the request,
they would come to his aid.
I realize you're
ambitious, Michitomo,
however, the prospect of
taking down Hirate‐dono
is virtually impossible.
Nothing can be done.
[MICHITOMO grunts]
It's not about ambition.
It's bigger.
This is about safeguarding
the future of the Oda clan.
[roars]
[groans]
What is it, old man?
Hey.
Ow!
Your guard's down!
Cheat!
[laughs]
Like it or not, you still
haven't gotten the better of me!
Right! One more bout!
Don't expect me
to hold back anymore.
[HIRATE]
I certainly hope not.
Old guy's lucky.
He can serve Nobunaga‐sama.
Meanwhile, I have to wait
until I come of age.
If you want to be useful, start
by attending to the horses.
Ow, hey!
Yeah. All right.
[MICHITOMO]
Inuchiyo!
This way!
Over here!
[gasps]
Not Hirate‐sama?!
Keep your voice down
or someone might hear!
It's true.
Turns out the old man's
been exploiting
his position as guardian.
Helping himself to
the Oda family's assets
behind our backs!
You can't be serious!
[MICHITOMO]
Shh!
Where's the proof?
That's the part where
you come into play.
This is for the good
of the Oda clan.
Got it?
[TOSHIIE]
Hmm...
For only a retainer,
he lives a luxurious lifestyle.
I wonder if what
Michitomo‐sama said was true.
Hope not.
[OHANA]
What are you doing in here?
You scared me!
No one's supposed to be here.
I was stopping by to drop
off a tea set I borrowed.
How come you're sneaking around?
I can't say!
Not even to me?
Sorry, but it's a
secret investigation.
Oh?
Into what?
Actually, Hirate‐sama
is under suspicion
of pocketing Oda family assets.
I'm looking for proof.
[OHANA chuckles]
You're kidding.
I would never, my lady!
Take a look at this!
How would he acquire
these pricey tea sets?
Those are from my late father.
Every piece displayed
on that shelf is a reward
for his unwavering
loyalty and service.
They're rewards?
You may not know this, but
the man you're accusing doted
on Nobunaga more
than anybody else.
My brother was
a temperamental child,
who everyone else wrote off.
But it was Hirate who
served as his teacher.
Nobunaga only
knows swordsmanship
and how to ride a horse
because he taught him.
And back when my brother was
injured falling off his steed,
it was Hirate who
made a commotion,
insisting that he himself
was the one to blame.
So, you see...
Hirate‐sama loves our lord
like he was his own son
and there's no possible way
he would ever
betray his trust!
You fool!
You were manipulated too easily!
Enough.
Be gone.
[SERVANT A]
Sorry. Don't mind us.
[MICHITOMO]
What's going on?
[SERVANT A] One of
Nobutomo‐sama's messengers
has arrived.
What? From Kiyosu?
[KICHOU] At this time, Owari was
governed from Kiyosu Castle
by the Yamato no Kami house,
Principal Line of the Oda Clan.
After the passing of
Nobuhide‐sama,
relations between its leader,
Nobutomo‐sama,
and Nobunaga‐sama
were strained to say the least.
[MESSENGER]
The recent uprising at Narumi
has been exceedingly
regrettable.
Nobutomo‐sama asks
how you're prepared
to accept responsibility
for such an immense failure.
In other words?
If he's suggesting Nobunaga‐
sama commit seppuku,
he's mad!
He doesn't want
anything that extreme.
However, he is wondering if
Nobuhide‐sama's successor
isn't proving to be
somewhat unreliable.
Uh?!
Him and me both.
My lord!
[NOBUNAGA] I wish to ask
Nobukatsu's opinion as well.
If there's no further business,
let's break for the day.
We must act.
It's political, not personal.
[HIDESADA] If the Lord Auditor
insists on ignoring us,
we can have the Principal Line
in Kiyosu replace the boy.
[MICHITOMO]
Uh...
I knew you'd think of a way.
Being reprimanded by
the Principal Line like that
casts him in a very bad light.
Wouldn't it be best
for everyone involved
if he allowed Nobukatsu‐sama
to replace him?
I agree completely.
Unlike someone
else I could name,
Nobukatsu‐sama demonstrates
a sense of decorum.
And he wouldn't force
impossible challenges upon us.
The Oda clan would have peace.
[HIRATE]
I wonder about that.
Huh?
[HIDESADA]
Hirate‐dono!
If Nobuhide's line is
considered undependable,
you should ask
yourselves "Why?"
Could it be because
of his son's disposition,
or because a leader is only
as effective as the retainers
he keeps by his side.
Are you implying
this is our fault?
A missive was sent to Kiyosu.
And the author is
someone from this castle.
[HIRATE]
If we don't work together
for the sake of the Oda clan,
it will fall into ruin.
Be aware that even now,
Nobuhide‐kou's eyes
are gazing down on us
from the heavenly realm.
Pretty good.
[SERVANT A]
Did you hear the rumor?
Apparently
Nobunaga‐sama's relations
with the Principal Line
have been shaky recently.
I heard they ordered him
to hand over control to
Nobukatsu‐ sama .
There's no way!
How could things
have gotten to this point?
How long have you been in here
and how much have you eaten?
[STABLEMAN A] Originally
this side of the family
was a subordinate lineage.
But then Nobuhide‐sama
eventually wound up
running the entire
show here in Owari.
Short version, the
Principal Line doesn't like it.
So hold on, this is
just about harassment?
They think they're so special.
The Principal Line.
Owari's only at peace
because of Nobunaga‐sama,
meanwhile those
high bloods didn't do squat.
If they say anything
else about my lord,
I'll let them know
exactly how I feel!
You're a headstrong one,
aren't you, Inuchiyo?
Believe it.
And I'd have no problem
laying down my life.
As long as it's for
Nobunaga‐sama.
[sighs]
[NOBUNAGA]
That so?
The kid really
said all those things?
Inuchiyo wasn't the only one.
I suspect that the entire castle
has been feeling on edge lately.
Truth be told, I've been feeling
a little bit suffocated myself.
Tsuneoki.
What do you say?
Heh.
An excellent idea.
What're you planning?
Matasaburou wins!
What on earth are they doing?
Sumo, my lady.
Don't you have this in Mino?
Of course!
But what I want
to know is why sumo?
It helps blow off steam.
Whether you're just
watching or grappling,
you end up feeling refreshed.
Nobunaga‐sama!
You should come over here!
[NOBUNAGA]
I think I will!
You mean you're going
to wrestle too, my lord?
[NOBUNAGA]
You better believe it.
And you can't win at sumo
unless you're using this.
[TAKIGAWA]
On the west side: Inuchiyo!
On the east: Kazusa no Suke!
[TAKIGAWA]
All right, then.
If both grapplers are ready,
begin!
[gasps]
Almost! Keep going!
Pivot your hips, my lord!
[TAKUGEN]
Are you all right?
I'm sorry you had to
see this, Takugen Oshou.
It appears you've caught me at
a rather embarrassing moment.
It appears to me
you're suffering
from quite a severe illness.
Nonsense.
It's because of
this intolerable heat.
There's no need to lie.
Simply go and
inform Nobunaga‐sama
that you're planning to
take a leave of absence.
I made a promise.
One so important, taking time
off to rest isn't an option.
It must be fulfilled,
at any cost.
Perhaps, but if you
continue behaving recklessly,
it's doubtful you'll
live to see it through.
That's the price I'll pay.
For the good of the Oda clan, I
would gladly sacrifice my life.
[SUMO C] Well done, my lord!
I knew you'd take him.
Sit down before you wear me out.
You ought to listen
to Yoichi, ya know?
Worrying can be
detrimental to your health.
How can I be calm
at a time like this?
I'm the head of the Oda
Yamato no Kami household!
And when I dispatch a
messenger, how am I met?
With the sound of crickets!
[DAIZEN]
Hmm...
You'll agree, they
should be chastised
for their lack of respect.
Huh?
After all, you're the most
powerful man in Owari.
It sounds like they need
to be reminded.
Sure, but brute force
isn't really how
we should go about it.
I'd prefer if we stuck
to diplomacy instead.
What's wrong, Nobutomo‐san?
You're not scared, are you?
[NOBUTOMO gasps]
Nobuhide's son needs
to be dealt with.
And I'm afraid
there's no other way.
The Yamato no Kami line
has justice on its side.
Worrying would be irrational.
[KICHOU]
August 15th, 1552.
Pressured by his
retainer Sakai Daizen,
Oda Nobutomo attacked both
Matsuba and Fukada Castle.
He took Nobunaga‐ sama 's
uncle, Nobutsugu‐ sama ,
as a hostage.
[HIDESADA] The way of
the samurai is to keep faith
with one's lord.
At this point, I believe we
must show our allegiance
to the Kiyosu Oda line.
How can you say that?
Our one and only lord is
sitting in front of us!
If you truly believe in honor,
we should defeat anyone who
opposes Nobunaga‐sama!
Mind your tongue, Inuchiyo!
Who are you to contradict
the Cavalry Guard?
Michitomo.
Perhaps it slipped your mind,
but this spring,
I came of age, and my name
was officially changed to
Maeda Matazaemon Toshiie.
And as Nobunaga‐sama's
attendant,
I'll ask that you address me
by my proper title.
[MICHITOMO]
How dare you!
So what do you think?
Retaking both castles
wouldn't prove difficult.
However, the problem is
defying the Principal Line.
By doing so,
I have no doubt we'll be
branded as a pack of rebels.
My thoughts too.
[gasps]
What?
The old man!
He collapsed at Tsushima while
on his way back from Sakai.
[TSUNEOKI]
There's no time to delay!
Hurry!
[NOBUNAGA]
Old man!
Nobunaga‐sama!
Please don't try to get up.
You need to rest.
[HIRATE] I hear both Matsuba
and Fukada were captured.
[NOBUNAGA] An ear to
the ground, just like always.
I imagine you feel
conflicted, my lord.
Questioning whether
to stir up trouble
with the Principal Line
in Kiyosu or not.
Heh. How do you see straight
to the heart of a problem?
[HIRATE]
I have something to ask.
Please, will you listen
to my final wish?
Don't say "final." I'll listen
to any number of wishes.
[HIRATE]
Long ago.
I made an agreement with
your father, Nobuhide‐sama,
and swore that
I would devote my life
to teaching you all the
skills you would need
in order to be his successor
and a worthy leader.
No matter who your
opposition turns out to be,
promise me you'll
always fight your hardest.
Fight to protect the Oda clan!
[NOBUNAGA]
I promise.
Please, don't try
to talk anymore, old man.
[TAKUGEN] Hirate‐dono
has been battling this illness
for several years.
Even though I recommended
immediate treatment,
he insisted his commitment
to you needed to be fulfilled.
And giving his life was
a small price to pay.
What commitment?
[YARAJ]
Are you Nobunaga‐sama?
Yes.
[YARAJ]
I've journeyed here
to deliver the cargo
Hirate requested I bring.
Two hundred fifty
muskets in total.
I have a deep
respect for Hirate.
When I promise him something,
I follow through.
What?
Old man.
You did this.
I swear I'll embrace your wish.
[TAKIGAWA]
My lord.
Great. Thanks.
They have muskets?
Stop your cowering!
That weapon can't
be fired repeatedly!
Now's the time to
let loose the arrows!
What the‐‐
[NOBUNAGA]
Just like that.
Break into squads of three: one
shooter and two men reloading.
If you understand,
begin firing immediately!
A nonstop assault
of musket fire.
I see.
So this was the strategy
he was exhaustively planning.
[HIRATE]
My lord.
Continue to soar.
And let this old man
be your springboard.
Upwards to greater
and greater heights.
All forces, advance!
Everybody's so intense!
And I'm not going to
let anyone show me up!
[KICHOU] In the end,
the battle achieved its goal.
Not only was
Nobunaga‐sama successful
in recovering both Matsuba
and Fukada Castles,
it's said his army advanced
all the way to Kiyosu
and burned the surrounding
fields, leaving the land barren.
[NOBUNAGA]
Old man!
I've just returned!
I'm...
[TAKUGEN]
This is a heartless era.
For now, all you can do is
focus on navigating beyond
the injustice and turbulence
that constantly surround us.
Yes.
[NOBUNAGA]
Just watch me, old man.
Watch how
I protect the Oda clan.