Is that you?
Father!
It's me.
Nobukatsu!
Please, I need to know!
Why?
Why was I allowed to live?
Father!
Brother?
[moans]
[screams]
Nobukatsu‐sama?
Nobukatsu‐sama!
Calm yourself!
Come, let's go
back to your room.
Heard the rumor?
They say a shade
roams the castle
during the ox‐hour at night.
I have.
I assume you're referring
to the one everyone claims
is an evil spirit.
A what?
I hope not.
A haunted castle is
far from a good omen.
[KATSUIE]
Same for me.
Nobukatsu‐sama won't see me.
The rumor is he's unwell
in both his mind and his body.
His defeat in the recent battle
certainly isn't helping.
As well as Nobunaga‐ sama 's
refusal to punish him.
He's haunted by the
thought of living in shame.
[HIDESADA]
I understand how he feels.
Yet in his state,
is he not merely a puppet
in Tsuzuki's hands?
Good morning, my lord.
My dreams;
they're dark as of late.
Dreams; they're
of no consequence.
Trust me, you'll be fine.
I feel this is an ideal time for
us to carry out a new strategy.
Do you now?
I'll make the
necessary arrangements.
There's no need to concern
yourself with any aspect of it.
Oh.
[TSUZUKI] You may be as
useless as a wooden doll,
but a skilled retainer can
orchestrate even your success.
What's the matter?
My Kurando.
Why do I always find
comfort in your darkness?
[TSUZUKI]
Darkness?
[NOBUNAGA]
Assassination?
[TSUNEOKI]
Yes.
The serpent uproar was a front
arranged by a group
within Suemori Castle
with the intent to bring
about your death.
We need to hem in.
Surveil the castle.
No.
The status quo is fine.
You mean you're just going
to let them go unchecked?
We don't know when
they'll try striking again!
[NOBUNAGA]
What proof do you have?
Well, I‐‐
Harboring suspicions
leads nowhere.
When you've found evidence,
then let me know.
[TSUNEOKI, TOSHIIE]
Yes.
Suemori won't give up.
I know they're
plotting something.
All we can do
is be ready for it.
Damn it!
We're surrounded
by enemies on all sides!
The Imagawa, Saitou, Iwakura.
Now this!
[NOBUNAGA] Can my brother and I
mend things between us?
Impossible to say.
If so, there's no telling
how long it could take.
Years?
[sighs]
I can't believe
she left this behind.
What's this?
The names of the people
who died in the battle, my lord.
I see.
My apologies if I've troubled
you with this business.
[NOBUKATSU] There's still
something I have to do.
[KICHOU] Around this time, at
Tsuneoki‐ dono 's insistence,
a special elite force
was formed
for the purpose of
protecting Nobunaga‐ sama .
They were called
the Cloaked Guard.
[chuckles]
Check me out!
Not bad!
You know, that cloak
would be extremely useful
for carrying your
head back home in.
[gasps]
[laughter]
Settle down.
They suit every last one of you.
Never bring shame to your armor.
Carry out your duty!
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
Pardon, my lord.
You've a guest
from the Ikoma estate.
[NOBUNAGA]
Huh? Kitsuno‐dono?
My lord,
the truth is Kichou‐ sama
visited my home recently.
[gasps]
She did?
When was this?
It must've been a few days ago.
To say that I was surprised
would be an understatement.
What reason would
Nobunaga‐ sama 's wife have
to come calling on me?
But the more we spoke, the more
powerfully my heart was shaken.
[KICHOU]
For certain reasons.
I must depart the Oda household.
Unfortunately,
it coincides with a dire time
in Nobunaga‐ sama 's life.
Though we met only by
chance during that battle,
I have an earnest request.
I place my hopes
with you, Kitsuno‐ sama .
In my absence,
I want you to become the
pillar that holds up his spirit.
I beg of you.
Please do this!
It was her eyes.
They were so large and clear,
I realized I had
seen them before.
That's when I knew
she was the warrior
who saved my life
in the midst of battle.
Huh? Warrior?
[KITSUNO]
During the course of business,
I got caught in the battle
at Inou Village
along with my attendants
and a customer.
[NOBUNAGA] You're telling me
you met her during the battle?
Kitsuno‐dono.
I'm sorry, but could you
leave me for the time being?
[gasps]
Of course.
[TSUZUKI]
In closing,
that's the stratagem
I propose we carry out.
You've explained it
clearly, Tsuzuki‐ dono .
I cannot endorse this plan.
[RETAINERS gasp]
And why not?
[KATSUIE] Because such
methods are cowardly.
What's more, even
if we use Ikeda‐ dono .
Nobunaga‐ sama 's
not guaranteed to show up.
What are your thoughts
on the matter, my lord?
He's already given
my plan his full approval.
I refuse to be involved
in this scheme. Excuse me.
Shibata‐dono!
Shibata. May I?
[KATSUIE]
My lord.
Nobukatsu‐ sama ,
it's been far too long.
I was glad to see you today.
Yes.
[KATSUIE]
I was rude earlier.
Tsuzuki.
You're not fond of him.
No.
We've known each other since
the days of my father's rule.
I have a favor to ask of you.
[KATSUIE]
Name it, my lord.
[PAGE C pants]
Ikeda‐dono!
A swift horse has arrived
from one of
Youtokuin‐ sama 's attendants.
[gasps]
What's the matter?
There's news of
my mother's health.
Her condition's taken
a turn for the worse.
I need to be with her.
Youtokuin‐sama?
That's just terrible!
I'm setting out immediately.
Please, do not tell
Nobunaga‐ sama about this.
Why not?
Surely he'd want to know.
I mean, Youtokuin‐ sama
was his wet nurse.
It's too risky for him to be
making any long journeys!
So, you've approved
of my stratagem.
A wise decision.
The first stage of the plan
is proceeding as arranged.
[TOSHIIE]
Nobunaga‐sama!
It's Ikeda‐dono!
They have him!
A message was sent saying
Youtokuin‐ sama was near death.
He rode out to
check her condition.
It was a ruse.
Damn!
Where is this Seikaku Temple?
They demand I come.
We believe it's abandoned,
near Isshiki Village.
[RETAINERS snickers]
[TSUZUKI chuckles]
When an exceptional
retainer is visited by death,
a lord's fate suddenly
becomes precarious.
Ikeda‐ dono has been
bound and confined.
Now we wait for Nobunaga
and his companions.
They should be
arriving very soon.
Our forces,
led by Shibata‐ dono ,
will intercept them.
After that,
it shouldn't take long
to rout his hastily
assembled squad.
As for his head.
I'll leave that
for you to remove.
[laughs]
That expression on your face.
It's been some time
since I've seen you
so full of vigor, my lord.
Truly, a beautiful sight.
[TSUZUKI]
What is this?
Please explain what's going on.
[TSUZUKI]
What is this?
Please explain what's going on.
The role you have played
has come to an end.
Your puppet's broken free.
What are you saying, my lord?
I continuously supported you.
Everything I did
was for the Oda clan!
Don't you dare speak of the Oda.
I require no intermediary
between me and my brother.
Listen to me!
Think back on
everything I did for you!
Who was always there by your
side, no matter what happened?
Without me,
you wouldn't have survived!
The only reason you're
still alive is because of me!
I'm perfectly aware,
to my utmost shame.
[gasps]
Leave.
If you insist on remaining
among the Oda,
I'll cut you down
using this blade.
[screams]
[NOBUNAGA]
Why do this, Nobukatsu?
If Tsuneoki's fallen victim
to your vengeance,
I'll never be able
to forgive you!
[NOBUKATSU] Let the
darkness flee into darkness.
We expected your arrival.
Where is Tsuneoki?
[NOBUKATSU]
Don't worry.
We haven't taken his head yet.
[NOBUNAGA]
Nobukatsu!
What are your intentions?
[NOBUKATSU]
If you wish to know, follow me.
It's a trap, my lord.
[NOBUNAGA]
I'm going alone.
Don't move from here.
You can't.
Leave this to Nobunaga‐sama.
[NOBUKATSU] Are you that
concerned about Tsuneoki?
[NOBUNAGA] If something happened
to him, don't expect any mercy!
[NOBUKATSU]
Hmph.
[NOBUNAGA]
What's the matter with you?
These are the
actions of a coward!
If there was something
you hoped for,
you should've come
to me directly!
[NOBUKATSU]
What hope?
That perished a long time ago.
Along with Hidetaka.
[NOBUNAGA]
Hidetaka?
What do you mean by that?
[NOBUKATSU] Even after the death
of our innocent younger brother,
you refused to join us
in battle to avenge him.
[gasps]
Because...
...I thought of what our
deceased father would have done.
How could I forget?
Yes.
It was the same
when Father died.
You chose not to
show up for the funeral.
Do you know how much I‐‐
[NOBUNAGA]
Yes, and I'm sorry.
[NOBUKATSU]
As if you would ever change.
You take the liberty of
behaving however you wish.
Even when people
criticize you, you don't care.
It's unthinkable.
Trusting the Oda clan
to the likes of you,
when I'm better suited
to lead the family.
Yet, both in commanding
on the field and in popularity,
I am no match for you.
[laughter]
[TSUNEOKI]
Nobunaga‐sama.
May you come to no harm.
[yelling]
[TOSHIIE]
Damn it.
I can't tell what's going
on from down here!
How long are
we supposed to wait?
[NOBUKATSU]
I have a favor to ask.
I'm going to banish Tsuzuki.
Also, I wish to speak
with my brother alone.
Assist me in this.
[KATSUIE] Nobukatsu‐ sama 's
volition has returned.
But will it lead
to good fortune or ill?
[NOBUKATSU]
Traitors are beheaded.
That's how it's done.
Yet you decided to let me live,
with no punishment whatsoever!
Can't you see?
You have saddled me with
a warrior's ultimate disgrace!
[NOBUNAGA]
You're wrong!
Listen!
I didn't think you needed
to lose your life over
a single mistake!
You call it a single mistake?
A battle where my honor
and life are on the line?
And you would write if off
completely‐‐as a simple mistake?
[NOBUNAGA]
No!
It wasn't to insult you!
I wanted the chance for us
to be brothers again!
That's your frailty speaking!
Though you were born
in a warrior household,
you reject the way!
[gasps]
Even if I don't cut you down,
eventually, someone close
to you will succeed.
It's strange.
I'm always caught in the middle,
wavering between
living as a warrior
and living for what
matters most to me.
[NOBUNAGA]
I'm constantly torn
between which direction
I should turn.
[NOBUNAGA]
What should I do?
I want to save both
you and Tsuneoki!
Is there a way to spare
your allies and enemies? No.
But maybe there is!
You mock me!
I truly mean it!
[NOBUKATSU]
Shut up!
You want to know the truth?
Tsuneoki is dead.
He fell by Tsuzuki's hand.
What?
[NOBUKATSU]
In exchange for his own life,
he begged us to
spare yours instead.
He died thinking of you.
A truly admirable death,
but ultimately in vain.
[laughs]
Ready yourself!
[screams]
[NOBUNAGA]
Nobukatsu!
[NOBUKATSU]
Nobunaga!
Elder brother!
[NOBUNAGA]
My beloved younger brother.
Nobukatsu! Nobukatsu!
Why?
Why did you halt
your sword strike?
[TSUNEOKI]
Nobunaga‐sama!
Tsuneoki!
You're unharmed!
Is he...?
[KATSUIE gasps]
Nobukatsu‐sama!
Someone, treat his wound!
There's no need.
It's done.
[NOBUNAGA]
Save your strength!
I've a request.
All that has happened,
lay the blame on me alone.
I understand, but you won't die!
On me alone.
Otherwise, these
wounds won't ever heal.
[NOBUNAGA]
Yes.
I swear.
[NOBUKATSU] I always admired you
and wanted to be by your side.
[NOBUNAGA]
I know. Don't speak.
[inaudible]
Elder brother.
Nobukatsu?
Nobukatsu!
This is what he wanted
from the start!
To end division and bring
the Oda clan together!
[gasps]
[NOBUKATSU]
I entrust this letter,
reflecting all of my sincerest
feelings, to Hidetaka.
Though we are brothers by blood,
over the course of time,
I feel a great distance
has grown between us.
However.
I haven't lost faith.
[NOBUKATSU]
Faith that the two of us,
who once looked up
to our father
and dreamed of becoming
just like him,
can bring our hearts together as
one and make a new beginning.
[KICHOU]
This was the manner in which
the forthright
Nobukatsu‐ sama died.
In the aftermath,
Nobunaga‐ sama granted
Nobukatsu‐ sama 's final wish,
and laid the blame
solely on him,
sparing his
brother's retainers
and bringing them
under his employ.
[giggles]
[NOBUNAGA] Somehow, he
looks like my younger brother.