[NOBUMORI]
Pull!
Use all your strength!
And pull!
[MURAI]
Nobunaga‐sama!
[NOBUNAGA]
How's the work?
[MURAI]
Going well.
As for Nakashima Fortress,
we should be finished
before the rainy season.
[KICHOU
1560.
Judging Imagawa Yoshimoto's
invasion to be imminent.
Nobunaga‐ sama bolstered
five fortresses along the border
in preparation for the assault.
[TAKUGEN] It's a difficult
journey getting past
all those strongholds.
[TSUNEOKI]
Takugen Oshou!
You've come far.
Why are you here?
I've heard a rumor.
Apparently trouble is
brewing with the Imagawa.
There have been
periodic spats with them
since my father's time.
We will drive them
back yet again.
Would you remind me,
exactly how long has it
been since you came of age?
Huh?
Fourteen years.
[TAKUGEN]
That many?
A great time has passed,
and you've accumulated
sufficient experience
to be in your prime.
If you're done with
the roundabout talking,
get to the point.
What is it you want?
In the realm of Suruga,
there once was a priest
I looked up to as a mentor.
His name was Taigen Sessai.
A strategist who covertly
supported Imagawa Yoshimoto.
One could say without
Master Sessai's efforts,
Imagawa's alliance
with the Takeda of Kai
and the Houjou of Segami
would never have existed.
However,
Master Sessai has passed
from this world into the next.
Now, Imagawa Yoshimoto is like
a beast, having lost all reason.
This will likely turn
into a great war,
in which previous experience
will be utterly
useless as a guide.
Please ready yourself for this.
A great war, you say?
[PRIEST]
What're you doing?
The shrine precincts are
no place for a spear practice!
Oh. Sorry 'bout that.
What would compel you to behave
in such a reckless manner?
Well, you see.
I heard Nobunaga‐ sama was
getting mixed up with Imagawa,
so I couldn't just stand
around idly anymore.
It sounds like he needs you.
I beg you, go.
Once again,
I can be of use to my lord!
As things stood, we would've
been caught in a pincer!
So I said, I said.
"My lord! Please
pull back from there!"
And there I am, spear in hand,
thrusting down one
Imagawa right after the other.
Long story short, that's how I
defended Nobuhide‐ sama 's life!
It's that time of the night.
Nobumori's tales of valor.
It's necessary to take them
with a grain of salt.
After all, in one story,
he "knocked down
a stone mountainside
with nothing but
the thrust of his spear!"
Surely, you're kidding.
He believes his own nonsense?
Huh?
There's our Reijirou!
[SASSA]
Come over!
Have a drink with us!
A word, alone.
Don't worry.
Go ahead.
Very well.
Imagawa is readying
his troops short of Mikawa.
Total, 10,000.
Uh?! Ten thousand?
So many, you must be mistaken.
Is it true?
It is.
I saw them myself.
That's for real?
And what numbers do we have?
Scraping together everyone,
2,000, optimistically.
[NOBUMORI] What will you do,
Nobunaga‐ sama ?
[nervous chatter]
I need to reflect
for a short while.
[HIDESADA] We've never
been invaded by an enemy force
on a scale of this size before.
We don't stand a chance when
we're outnumbered five to one!
What about sealing
ourselves up for a siege?
Without the prospect of
acquiring reinforcements?
We can't win.
What if we make peace with Mino
and ask for their assistance?
That's counteracting
poison with more poison.
Saitou Yoshitatsu.
He's very cunning.
If we show any sign of weakness,
he's sure to assail us.
[groans]
Don't we have
any allies anywhere?
Maybe so!
Nobukiyo‐dono?
I have an idea, my lord.
Look at this.
A receipt?
Hattori Tomosada‐dono.
I believe the man is chief
over a group of monks
headquartered in Ninoue.
He's not to be trusted.
Not once since
Nobuhide‐ sama 's era
has he shown
allegiance to anyone.
That's true, but he's had
dealings with us at Inuyama.
The receipt is
clearly proof of that.
I've heard stories before.
How the buccaneers of Ninoue
control a thousand warships.
If they were our allies.
Imagine.
We could trap Imagawa
from land and sea.
All right.
Ask him.
Leave everything to me.
[KICHOU] However,
the negotiations failed.
Judging the outlook of
the Oda army to be grim.
Hattori Tomosada instead
sealed an alliance with Imagawa.
You've gone and made us
even more enemies!
Not on purpose.
[SASSA pants]
This is bad!
Calm down and
tell us what's wrong.
[SASSA]
It's Imagawa!
His army has entered Mikawa!
Already?
It's too soon!
[SASSA]
By the way,
where's Nobunaga‐sama?
No matter how many books
on strategy I page through,
there's no method for defeating
an enemy of this magnitude.
While that may be true,
taking a leisurely stroll isn't
going to help us either.
Let's return to the castle.
[NOBUNAGA]
A swallow.
It's gonna rain soon!
Huh? One second!
Huh?
How are you certain
it's going to rain?
Doesn't everyone know?
You can tell because
all of the swallows
are flying low to the ground.
I'll remember that.
[BOY B] Samurai‐ san ,
you should hurry home too.
There's no greater strength
than experience.
I completely forgot about the
most important resource I had.
[NOBUNAGA]
Where am I?
How'd I get here?
[NOBUKATSU]
Elder Brother.
[NOBUNAGA]
Nobukatsu!
[gasps]
Wait, Father!
If you're both alive,
then I'm... dreaming.
Why are you crying,
Elder Brother?
[NOBUNAGA]
I'm in this field.
Young again.
And it seems that
I'm learning the basics
of falconing with Kanjuurou.
Listen.
In order to capture your prey,
the first step is to let
them become careless.
How do I do that?
[NOBUHIDE]
Vanish into the trees and grass.
Match your breath to the wind's
rhythm, until the prey appears.
Be still and wait.
There!
Not yet.
Draw it in nearer.
[NOBUNAGA]
We got it!
Father, look!
[NOBUNAGA]
Father.
Is something wrong?
I was having a dream.
A dream?
In it, my father and Nobukatsu
taught me how to wage this war.
[NOBUNAGA]
Call them all here.
Imagawa's army is advancing.
But pushing for Kiyosu in a
single stroke seems unlikely.
Later.
When he's stationed
troops in Kutsukake,
he's likely to target Odaka
and Narumi Castles.
If so, presumably he'll move
his troops along ridgelines
that allow for good visibility.
Ten thousand's a force.
Naturally, the ranks
will be extended.
In other words,
Imagawa won't be
heavily protected.
I'd say he'll have
2,000 troops guarding him.
I see.
So we flank that point
and attack him?
Still, the general could be
anywhere within the ranks.
We won't know his location.
Yes, we will.
We'll meet Imagawa's vanguard
by equipping Washizu
and Marune Fortresses
with as many muskets
as we're able to transport.
With his superior numbers,
Imagawa will no doubt move
his main squad into the fray,
bent on crushing them
through sheer force.
And when he makes his move.
I'll strike him from
Nakashima Fortress.
One thing,
that fortress is clearly
visible from the ridgeline.
The enemy would realize
your strategy right away.
That's exactly
what my intention is.
[NOBUNAGA] Why do you
suppose Imagawa Yoshimoto,
the head commander,
is coming all the way out
to Owari in person?
Because he's rapacious.
He wants to see
with his own eyes.
To be present when a
great army under his command
stomps us out like insects.
So we'll lure him out.
While he's distracted,
watching for the moment
when I'm taken down.
We'll attack all at once!
If we pull it off, then we
might be able to defeat him.
There's no "might."
We absolutely can!
[approving chatter]
Make ready for battle!
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
[KICHOU]
June 11th, 1560.
Word arrived that
Imagawa Yoshimoto's army
had reached Kutsukake Castle.
Sakuma Nobumori, bolstering the
defenses of Zenshouji Fortress!
Follow me!
Father.
There's no need to worry.
This war will soon be over with.
Watch over your siblings.
I will!
There you are.
[SASSA]
Elder Brother!
You're riding to battle?
To Nakashima Fortress.
Well?
Are you going to ride with us
or besmirch the Cloaked Guard?
Who do you think
you're talking to?
[laughs]
[NOBUKIYO] What do mean
by ordering me back to Inuyama?
Are you saying that
I'd only get in the way?
I need you to keep Mino
from thinking they have
the chance to attack.
We'd have our backs exposed.
And thus wouldn't be
able to fight Imagawa
knowing they
were left unchecked.
I understand.
[KICHOU]
At this juncture,
Nobunaga‐ sama was confident
with his odds of winning.
That is... until Oda
reconnaissance sighted
the Imagawa army
crossing Kutsukake Pass.
Forty thousand?
Are you certain
this isn't some mistake?
It's confirmed.
Nearly all of Suruga's army
has been directed this way.
Also, there's Mikawa's troops,
they've joined with them.
That's 20 times the
number of our troops.
We're unable to contend
with that many.
Our only chance is
for a peace offering.
No. We fight.
Pardon?
We'll wait until they're
overextended, then strike.
That's the plan.
As their numbers increase, their
movements will grow sluggish,
and an opening will emerge.
I agree with Takigawa‐dono.
Let's fight!
My lord, against such
an enormous army,
both Marune and Washizu,
our two front lines of defense,
would be overrun immediately.
It doesn't matter
the number of troops!
Our soldiers' spirits
are stronger!
We've come too far
to back down now!
Now that you've made it
abundantly clear how you feel,
we've only to
combine our strength,
and we'll overcome
this trial together!
‐‐[ALL] Yes, sir!
‐‐[TSUNEOKI] But, my lord!
[KICHOU]
In all the time I've known him,
Nobunaga‐ sama has
never spoken hollow words.
[TSUNEOKI]
I've no idea what he's thinking.
Forward, men!
[KICHOU]
June 12th, 1560.
The Imagawa army's vanguard
overran Washizu Fortress.
Commanding the attack
was Matsudaira Motoyasu,
later known as
Tokugawa Ieyasu‐kou.
So, it has finally begun.
Imagawa's main force will very
likely begin pressing forward
starting tomorrow morning.
Then we'll have no choice
but to launch our attack
on this army of 40,000.
And you're sure this
is what you wish to do.
Yes, I am, and It will
be my final request.
Just making sure.
I once made a wager with
your father, Nobuhide‐ kou .
Whether one day you would bring
all of Japan under your sway.
I never took you
to be a betting man.
And?
Which side did you wager on?
If I said, it'd only serve
to irritate you.
[laughs]
[WATCHMAN]
They're here!
If they want a fight,
they've got it.
They have the gall
to set foot on Owari soil.
Make them regret their decision!
[ARMY]
Yes, sir!
We've received word!
The Imagawa forces!
They've assaulted
Marune Fortress!
[gasps]
Where's Nobunaga‐sama?
[KICHOU]
Nowhere to be found.
What?
Whatever's going on, I can't
help but feel apprehensive.
What if he's planning
to offer his own head,
killing himself so Imagawa
will end this war?
Honestly, I was worried
about the same thing.
However excellent the strategy
is, we're so outmatched
damage to our own side
will be catastrophic.
Offering up his own life, so his
companions won't die needlessly.
That's just the sort of proposal
he would come up with.
Let's go!
We have to stop him!
Then I take it you know where
we can find Nobunaga‐sama?
Of course!
Tsuneoki‐dono!
Why are you dawdling around?
Don't you realize
your lord has already set out!
Sound the horns!
Huh? You heard him!
Let's get moving!
Ride!
Reporting, sir!
Maeda Toshiie.
Hastening to your side,
as promised!
I swear upon my name, as long
as I breathe, I will serve you.
Um, what's with
that outfit, my lord?
This is‐‐
I get it!
You're praying for victory!
Let me join you!
Listen to me.
Go back home to Kiyosu!
Go home?
Are you saying you don't
require my services?
You can't.
I want to fight on your behalf,
Nobunaga‐ sama !
Toshiie.
That smoke cloud, it's either
from Marune or Washizu.
I'm positive the men fighting
there feel the same as I do!
[TSUNEOKI]
Nobunaga‐sama!
Tsuneoki!
Yes.
I've come to accompany you.
My lord, did you really think
you could leave me behind?
[gasps]
[TSUNEOKI] I've spent more
than 20 years in your service.
Back when you were flamboyant.
When you bought all
the foreign goods you could.
And when you took someone
with an extraordinary
secret past as your wife.
Over the years, you've made
me suffer numerous hardships,
but this one is the worst.
Hold on.
[TSUNEOKI] Those men
who are clashing blades
at this very moment,
have faith in you.
They believe you'll build
a new world because
you've never been trapped
by the old order of thought.
They want to see that vista.
With their own eyes.
If you want to keep all their
hopes from falling into ruin,
then fight, Nobunaga!
[gasps]
Please, fight.
[sighs]
Tsuneoki, you saved me.
I was on the verge of being
pretentious and scatter‐brained.
[NOBUNAGA]
But it's still over.
In short,
I sent Takugen Oshou as a
messenger to broker for peace.
We'll stop him immediately.
[TAKUGEN]
Have you three finished talking?
Huh?
Takugen!
[TAKUGEN] I suspected events
would play out this way,
so I paused for a bit.
And the letter I gave
you to pass along?
Forgive me, but I never had
any intention of delivering it.
You see, I do
dislike losing wagers.
[KATSUIE]
Nobunaga‐sama!
As retainers of the Oda clan,
we will accompany you
wherever you choose to go.
All of us will.
So, whaddaya say?
Will somebody
please bring me food?
I haven't eaten
since last night,
since I thought I'd be
cutting open my stomach.
My Lord.
A swallow!
Somehow,
I suspect it'll rain soon.
With the heavens as our allies,
there's no doubt
as to our victory!
[NOBUNAGA ARMY]
Yes, sir!
[IMAGAWA RETAINER A]
Imagawa‐sama.
We've received word
that both Washizu and Marune
Fortresses have fallen.
[IMAGAWA]
Hmm...
It looks like rain.
Fine.
We'll rest a while.
Sir!
Prepare the camp!
[NOBUNAGA] Listen carefully
and heed my words!
Luck is for Heaven to decide!
If they charge, retreat.
If they fall back,
press forward!
And if we're victorious.
History will remember those
of you who fought here today!
I swear, your names will
echo through eternity!
Ride with me!
Don't let these
little fish distract you!
Our target is the head
of Imagawa Yoshimoto!
[KICHOU]
Thus, on that day,
during the battle at Okehazama,
Nobunaga‐ sama
killed Imagawa Yoshimoto.
Just over ten years
after his first battle,
hemmed in by powerful realms,
and amidst endless strife
within his own land and home,
he fought with champions
at his side and survived.
This occurred in the spring
after his 27th birthday.