[KICHOU]
May 1556.
Saitou Dousan,
along with his eldest son,
Saitou Yoshitatsu,
fell to warring.
Though Nobunaga‐ sama
dispatched troops in support,
it was too late.
Saitou Dousan, the Viper
of Mino, had been slain.
No, Father.
[gasps]
Another dream
about Dousan‐ dono ?
Yes.
In this one he was encircled by
a snake and engulfed in flames.
He never treated me
like his own child.
After all this time,
I still resent him.
Why am I hurting?
Despite that,
he was your father.
It's only natural you
would grieve losing him.
Kichou.
You said you were bitter
towards him in this life.
And yet, when somebody passes,
they need to be forgiven.
Let go of the pain and
forgive Dousan‐ dono .
Thank you for that, my lord.
[yawns]
Huh?
What's the matter?
Let's hurry home
and get some dinner.
[VILLAGER A]
You've gotta be hungry too.
[VILLAGER A] Why'd all the
birds stop chirping?
What else could go wrong today?
[OX moos]
[VILLAGER A grunts]
[VILLAGER A screams]
[KICHOU] Nobunaga‐ sama
continued to be plagued
by headache‐inducing
circumstances.
One situation involved Oda
Ise no Kami Nobukata‐ sama ,
lord of Iwakura castle,
conspiring
with Saitou Yoshitatsu,
to push Nobunaga into a corner.
Furthermore, Oda Nobukiyo‐ sama
of Inuyama Castle
began showing signs
of going his own way.
[NOBUNAGA]
Even though I don't want war,
it doesn't seem to matter.
It's one thing right
after another.
All right, then,
let's hear solutions.
How about this?
Have you thought of something
ingenious, Toshiie?
There's a serpent.
They say it's in
Midori‐ga‐Ike Pond.
[NOBUNAGA]
A serpent?
Listen to this.
Apparently this beast
is so massive,
it was able to drag a whole ox
under water with no problem.
Sorry.
And this is relevant
to our discussion, how?
It's not.
Then why did you bring it up
in the first place?
Hold on.
Kichou has had
a number of dreams
involving serpents lately.
That's considered
a good omen, my lord.
Perhaps it means you and
Kichou‐ sama can expect an heir
in the near future.
Huh? Hey, now.
It doesn't mean
anything like that.
[TOSHIIE]
This is cause for celebration!
Not you too.
Settle down.
Ow!
[laughter]
A serpent.
Huh.
[VILLAGER B] Have you
heard of the monster
living in Midori‐ga‐Ike Pond?
[VILLAGER C]
Yes!
They say that it
swallowed an ox!
[VILLAGER D]
You've gotta be crazy
if you think I'm going
anywhere near Midori‐ga‐Ike!
[NINJA A]
It's confirmed.
The rumor has spread
among the people.
[TSUZUKI] Then everything
is proceeding exactly
as we planned.
Don't hesitate to spend
as much money
as you deem necessary
marshalling others,
so we can get this rumor
traveling all across Owari.
I want to be absolutely sure it
reaches Nobunaga's ears.
Yes, sir.
[OHANA]
Huh?!
[NOBUNAGA]
Huh?
Elder Sister.
I heard the good news!
Our family's getting one more.
First off, you don't
wanna eat too much kelp.
They say it can be harmful
to a child in the womb.
This is starting
to get out of hand.
Kichou dreaming about snakes
doesn't mean anything.
Your brother is right.
I'm not expecting a child.
You've got this all wrong.
Look, when a woman knows,
she knows.
Now, listen, to ensure the
stability of the Oda house,
an heir is an
absolute necessity!
So take care of
your health, all right?
I found it!
In foreign lands,
there's a giant snake
referred to as a "python."
This must be the source of
the "great serpent" uproar.
The most likely scenario
is that this python somehow
escaped from Yaraj
and took refuge in the pond.
What's wrong?
It's um, nothing.
Forgive me if
I don't believe you.
Is there really a snake
large enough to do that?
Swallow an entire ox?
You don't think it's a snake?
I don't know, my lord.
[NOBUNAGA]
Are you still thinking
about what my
sister said earlier?
[KICHOU]
No.
[NOBUNAGA]
Then what is it?
I haven't borne a child,
and relations with Mino
have been completely severed.
There's no point in me being
here or staying by your side.
Do you truly believe that?
[gasps]
[NOBUNAGA] Even though I've
become the Defender of Owari,
I'm still surrounded by enemies.
I have no time to relax except
when I get to be alone
with you, like this.
Nobunaga‐sama.
At first our relationship
was purely political.
It's something else now.
You always ease my mind.
[KICHOU]
Is something wrong, my lord?
[NOBUNAGA]
I've got it!
What would I do without you?
[MORISHIGE]
I see.
We marry your sister
Oichi‐ sama to Nobukiyo‐ sama
in order to seal an alliance.
[NOBUNAGA] Right.
I remembered the other night
the source of my bond
with Saitou Dousan‐ dono
was Kichou becoming
part of our family.
[TOSHIIE]
Sure!
Nobukiyo‐ sama has
been estranged from you,
but if you could
improve relations,
it'd mean no more warring!
[NOBUNAGA]
Oichi.
I'm afraid we've moved ahead
without including you
in these discussions.
But it's for the good of Owari.
Please trust me.
Sorry, but there's
no way to broker peace
except marrying you to Nobukiyo.
If it's for your sake, Brother.
I'm glad to help
and become a bride.
Oichi.
[KICHOU]
Arrangements were made
for Oichi‐ sama to travel
to Nobukiyo‐ sama 's home.
[OHANA]
On this occasion,
into Nobukiyo‐ sama 's
keeping, our Oichi‐‐
Save the introductions.
I know it all from the letter.
Are you Oichi?
Yes, my lord.
So, you're still
only a child then?
[NOBUKIYO]
It's all right.
Come over here.
Huh?!
[NOBUKIYO]
I told you to come closer.
Oh, of course.
A little closer, please.
[OICHI]
Yes, my lord.
Ah!
A pity.
I can only describe
your looks as so‐so.
I apologize if they're
not to your liking.
[NOBUKIYO] Too early
for her to bear any children.
What?
Don't be nervous.
I can't leave Oichi
with a cad like you.
Have you no shame?
Why you...?!
[OHANA]
Hmph.
I'm so sorry!
Nobody can blame you
for the way you acted.
Going by everything I heard,
I would have slapped him myself.
I shouldn't have put
Oichi in that situation.
How is she handling it?
[OICHI sobs]
[OHANA]
The poor girl's in tears.
I guess it's safe to say
the engagement was
a complete failure?
Since you slapped the guy
she was supposed to marry.
What exactly are you
doing out here?
I want to know the
name of your employer.
Have faith, my lord.
It's important you
don't give up yet.
You can rest assured.
I, Tsuzuki, have already
taken the needed steps.
I swear I will
bring you good news.
[TSUNEOKI]
That talk about a giant snake,
it's no longer a joke.
The common folk of
Owari are all frightened.
They're saying nobody
will go near the pond now
out of fear of being eaten.
As things stand,
we can't ignore this anymore.
I may have a solution.
If this great serpent
actually does exist,
then all we need to do
in order to capture it
is to drain the pond.
A brilliant plan, my lord!
Without water,
the snake can't conceal itself,
making it easy for us to catch.
This could be
just the thing to lift
Ohana and Oichi's spirits too.
All right.
We leave for the pond tomorrow.
Is that so?
[NOBUNAGA]
Hmm?
What's the matter?
[TSUZUKI]
Ah.
It's Nobunaga‐sama.
The rumor of this pond's serpent
has spread all
throughout the land.
Nobukatsu said if
Owari's common folk were afraid,
then we ought to
capture the serpent
and put their minds at ease.
You don't say.
It's funny you
should mention that.
I was thinking
the exact same thing.
Where is Nobukatsu?
I'm afraid that my lord is
resting at Suemori Castle.
He took ill suddenly
and is convalescing.
Is that so?
Let's work together and capture
this beast for his sake, then.
Our retainers are working
to drain the pond of
its water as we speak.
Lend these men a hand.
What is this snake like anyway?
If it could swallow an ox whole,
it goes without saying it
must be gigantic!
That sounds terrifying!
[OHANA]
It is pretty scary.
[OICHI]
What if it tries eating us?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Nobunaga‐sama!
This way, please!
You can see well into
the pond from this angle.
[NOBUNAGA]
Right!
[gasps]
[KICHOU screams]
What happened?
[TSUNEOKI]
Kichou‐sama!
[TSUZUKI]
It seems the serpent
isn't making an
appearance today.
Let's wrap things up.
Not to worry, though.
I'm sure we'll have
better luck tomorrow.
Hopefully, you can join us then.
Of course.
Until tomorrow.
About what happened.
I wonder if it'll dry
by the time we get home.
Why did you pretend
to fall down earlier?
Whatever do you mean?
[TSUNEOKI] I know you
tripped on purpose, my lady.
Keep it a secret
from Nobunaga‐ sama .
[TSUNEOKI]
Why?
There was an assassin here.
Really?
Then this was planned
by Nobukatsu‐ sama ?
I can't say,
but if that's the case,
then I want to end this quickly.
Without my husband's knowledge.
Hey! We're headed back home!
Come on!
[KICHOU]
Yes, my lord.
Man, everyone's snake‐hunting
at Midori‐ga‐Ike pond.
Why do I have to stay
and hold down the fort?
I would've killed
to see it in person.
I finally found you,
Maeda‐ dono !
[TOSHIIE]
Huh?
[RETAINER]
I'm sorry.
It's Oda Nobukiyo.
He's here?
Direct him to
the reception hall!
He was in a
highly agitated state
and wanted to know
where Ohana‐ sama was.
What did you tell him?
When I said she'd
gone to Midori‐ga‐Ike
to see the serpent,
he rode in that direction.
[TOSHIIE] He wants
vengeance for that slap.
Who knows what he'll do.
He may even try
to kill Ohana‐ sama !
The weather's certainly
foggy today, isn't it?
[NOBUNAGA] We've nearly
drained the entire pond.
Soon the Serpent of Owari
will have nowhere to hide.
[TSUZUKI] It isn't the
right time to strike yet.
[NINJA C]
That wasn't us, sir.
[TSUZUKI]
Huh?
[KICHOU] So, they're
your men, as I guessed.
[TSUZUKI]
Reveal yourself, now.
[KICHOU] Pass this message
along to Nobukatsu‐ sama :
dispense with the
short‐sighted thinking.
Whatever happens,
I won't let you interfere
with Nobunaga‐ sama !
Well, now.
It's none other than
Nobunaga‐ sama 's honored wife.
Huh?
Is someone out there?
Nobukatsu‐ sama will be
Owari's supreme ruler, I swear!
[KICHOU] And I swear
to defend Nobunaga‐ sama !
[TSUZUKI]
I thought it was odd
when you stumbled near
the pond the other day.
Deceiver!
There you are!
You're hurt.
[KICHOU]
Why are you here?
[TSUNEOKI]
You're secret's safe.
Nobunaga‐ sama hasn't
discovered the truth yet.
You need treatment immediately.
I'm fine.
Let me.
Stop!
All those scars.
How did you...
[KICHOU]
Isn't it laughable?
Can you imagine
someone as damaged
as me being
by his side forever?
Wouldn't you scoff?
Never, my lady.
Then.
I suppose I'll scoff at myself.
[TSUNEOKI]
What's happened at this pond
was all a plot orchestrated
by Nobukatsu‐ sama .
We must inform Nobunaga‐sama.
[KICHOU] They've already
made their final attempt.
[TSUNEOKI]
Huh?
Curses.
Their guard is up now.
Did we fail?
[approaching hoofbeats]
Huh?
[OHANA]
Who is that?
Nobukiyo‐sama?
You've come a long way.
Why would you ride so far?
You'll share your
intentions this instant!
Let's not do anything rash!
[TOSHIIE]
Not good.
At this rate,
this will turn into a war!
You need to calm down,
Nobukiyo‐ dono !
[TSUZUKI]
Here's our chance.
[NINJA H screams]
What the...?!
The serpent wasn't
supposed to be real.
[NOBUNAGA]
Watch out! Behind you!
Look. I... Will you‐‐?
Get down!
Ohana!
[NOBUKIYO]
What is...?
No one touches her, got it?
Nobukiyo‐sama?
Bring the rope!
Let's bind this serpent!
[RETRAINERS groan
[muttering]
What's going on?
[NOBUKIYO] I've never met a
woman as strong‐willed as you!
Will you be my bride?
[gasps]
[KICHOU] And so it came
to be that Ohana‐ sama
would go on to wed
Oda Nobukiyo‐ sama
[KICHOU grunts]
[NOBUNAGA]
Huh?
Kichou?
I've thought something was wrong
since you stumbled in the pond.
What happened?
Nothing, truly.
It can't be nothing if you
sustained such a wound.
Really, it's just a scratch.
So, what about the python?
I heard about it from Yaraj,
and how you requested
that he release the serpent.
To what do you refer?
I know of no such thing.
You and I are
supposed to be close.
So how are there still secrets
you need to keep from me?
Please.
Tell me.
Nobunaga‐sama.
I really.
The truth is that I...
I just...
Kichou.
[NOBUNAGA]
What're you?
[KICHOU]
Listen closely.
I have a favor to ask of you.
[NOBUNAGA]
Name it.
Be happy, my lord.
Kitsuno‐ sama can
make that possible.
I don't understand
what you mean.
[NOBUNAGA]
Kichou!
Where're you going?
Come back!
Kichou!
[NOBUNAGA]
Don't leave.
You don't have any ideas
about her whereabouts?
Where she could have run off to?
Or why she decided to leave?
Nothing at all?
Why, Kichou?
Where did you go?
Not back to Mino.
There's no place
for her there anymore.
I refuse to concede.
Without fail, I will bring
death to Nobunaga
and make Nobukatsu
the supreme ruler of Owari.
No.
Nobukatsu is nothing
more than a puppet.
I will become the supreme ruler!
[laughs]