[KICHOU]
Father.
[DOUSAN]
Hmm?
Kichou.
Would you believe Oda
made a peace overture?
[KICHOU gasps]
Is that so?
It's hard to believe.
Nobuhide's illness must
be affecting his spirit.
This is an opportunity
I never dared hope for.
My daughter.
There's something important
I must ask of you.
Yes.
I'll do whatever it is you wish.
[KICHOU]
Oda Nobunaga.
When the world was at war,
he eclipsed it like a demon god.
Though much has
been written about him,
the man I knew differed
from the legend.
Tonight, let me tell
you a bit more about
who that Nobunaga‐sama
really was.
[NOBUNAGA splutters]
You want me to get married?
[TAKUGEN]
Yes.
We've already
waited far too long.
This stays between us,
but one or two offers
have already been extended
to your younger brother,
and I must say,
the matches are attractive.
You're kidding.
[WOMAN]
Isn't he dashing?
[TSUNEOKI] Kanjuurou‐sama's
garnering attention
thanks to his recent
growth spurt.
[NOBUNAGA]
That's what this is about?
He hasn't even come of age yet.
Nobunaga‐sama, you'll
forgive me for being so blunt,
but you are the heir
apparent to the Oda line.
You do not have
the luxury of waiting
for the right person
to come along.
As your advisors,
we've considered lineage
and the circumstances of Owari.
So then who?
Kichou‐dono, the darling
daughter of Saitou Dousan.
[splutters]
You'd pair me with
the daughter of "The Viper"?
[TSUNEOKI] Sealing an alliance
with Mino would allow us
to quell internal unrest.
And strengthen our stance
against Mikawa and Suruga.
You have to admit,
it's a win‐win.
Those are all good points.
But she's the Viper's Daughter!
I bet this is an accurate
rendering of her.
What is that, my Lord?
It's, uh...
I found you!
[gasps]
Oichi?
Good to see you.
[NOBUNAGA]
You're here too?
And what are the
two of you doing here?
Don't play coy!
We've come to celebrate
your marriage, of course!
Marriage! Marriage!
I just heard about it myself
and nothing's carved in stone.
Not to mention,
I haven't said "yes."
So what exactly are you saying?
If you don't act quickly,
she'll get snatched up
by somebody else!
Snatched up?
This is the Lady of Mino.
Renowned for being the greatest
beauty in the entire region.
Seriously?
So you don't have
a problem as long as
she has a pretty face?
Well, appearances are important.
You can't judge compatibility
until you've spent
some time together.
Once you're married,
you'll know.
You're enjoying
this way too much.
I'm simply cheering
you on as your big sister.
Wait.
Is there someone else
you have your heart set on
we don't know about?
Someone else?
Nah.
[OHANA]
Then it's settled!
[OICHI]
It's settled!
[TSUNEOKI]
You can't forget about her.
After all this time.
Sorry?
What're you talking about?
Ikoma‐ dono 's daughter,
who else?
[NOBUNAGA]
Doesn't ring a bell.
Even though you constantly
say her name in your sleep?
Mercy!
I give up, my lord!
[NOBUNAGA]
Actually,
I overheard my mother
saying something yesterday.
Kitsuno was married off.
Into the Miyake,
an influential clan.
That's a strange coincidence
or... Takugen Oshou's work.
If so, it's got me annoyed.
Are you going to let him know?
Annoyed with myself, you idiot.
My heart's chosen
politics over love.
I'm more drawn to the idea of
using marriage to quell unrest,
than I am to the girl
that I had feelings for.
It's my own heartlessness
that annoys me.
You may think it's heartless,
but I admire your
sense of responsibility.
Yeah. Right.
Still though, you get
how marrying someone
you've never seen would
make anyone a little nervous.
Hear me out.
Why do I have the
feeling you're devising
some kind of scheme?
[HIRATE]
Young master!
Where are you hiding?
[NOBUHIRO]
What's all the shouting about?
And this early.
[HIRATE] We can't find
your brother anywhere!
Strange.
[HIDESADA]
Tsuneoki's missing too!
Isn't it possible they
just went fishing or something?
If you mean Nobunaga,
he said he was riding off
to get a look at the
Lady of Mino's visage.
Huh?
[HIRATE]
He did what?
[VILLAGER A] Heh. You think
a couple of peasants like us
could get in to see the Lady?
Not in a million years!
Is that so?
Thank you for your time.
Have a good day.
Look!
It's the Lady!
[VILLAGER C]
You see her?
Over there!
[VILLAGER D]
Up on the watchtower!
[VILLAGER E] They say no other
woman compares to her beauty.
Apparently, she's so
gorgeous, if you saw her,
you'd mistake her for an angel.
Might as well be,
all the way up there.
There's no way
you're going to be able
to sneak a peek at her face.
True, but at least
we discovered something
useful on this trip.
Look around.
Even though we detest the
man and call him "The Viper."
He seems to be a
surprisingly decent ruler.
To this lot at least.
We should leave soon
before the sun sets, my lord.
Sure, in a minute.
[BRIGAND B]
Hey, you!
Why don't you watch
where you're going?
What?
No apology
after you ran into me?
We don't forgive so easily.
I'd say compensation's in order.
Let him go.
Huh?
Boy.
Nobody talks that way to us.
[BRIGAND B]
I don't care if you are a kid.
A different approach is needed.
[gunshot]
[FEMALE VILLAGER]
What is that thing?
[NOBUNAGA]
Stay or flee, it's up to you.
But you should know,
there're more lead balls
where that came from.
[BRIGAND A]
Let's get outta here!
Nobunaga‐sama.
Good thing they ran,
since I can only use this once.
The other problem is
with the barrel's length.
It's never hit a single target.
You realize you're terrible.
I know.
[laughter]
[BRIGAND A]
Over here!
They're coming back!
Let's go!
Yeah, but where?
[NOBUNAGA]
Who knows?
[sighs]
[TAKUGEN chuckles]
That boy never fails
to surprise me.
Who could've foreseen he'd be
unable to wait until the wedding
and would sneak off
to see the Lady of Mino?
This is no laughing matter!
Imagine if a mishap
were to occur!
The reconciliation with
Mino would be called off.
In addition to that,
it would give their forces a
pretext to cross the Kiso River.
I was saying it
from the very beginning.
If we were arranging a marriage,
it should have been
with Kanjuurou‐sama
and not his older brother.
Don't be unreasonable!
The boy hasn't come of age.
He's too young.
Sound the horns!
Now!
Assemble the troops!
We're rescuing Nobunaga!
All of you, follow me!
[HIRATE] Composure,
Nobuhiro‐sama! Please!
[KATSUIE] If we cross
the Kiso River with an army,
the war will start
all over again!
[HIDESADA]
We're advisors! Let us advise!
I'll lure them
further into the woods.
When you see an opening, run.
No. We're escaping together.
A retainer puts himself at risk
in order to protect his lord.
That's his job.
And I'm telling you,
if you gave up your
life to save mine,
the rest of my days would
be spent in torment.
[jingle]
[BRIGAND A laughs]
Did you drop something?
I'll carve you in half!
My lord!
[BRIGAND A roars]
Die!
[KICHOU]
Foolish rogues.
You do realize you're
on Mount Inaba,
which is under the
rule of Saitou Dousan?
And who the hell are you?
You got a death wish?
[BRIGAND B]
Fine. I'm going!
Wait!
Nobunaga‐sama!
I'm all right.
[KICHOU]
Nobunaga?
Tsuneoki!
[KICHOU]
What are you doing here?
I was.
[KICHOU]
Answer me!
I came to gaze upon the
face of the Lady of Mino.
[KICHOU gasps]
No!
Please.
Please wake up!
No, this can't be happening.
[DOUSAN]
Who'd you say?
You mean Nobuhide's
idiot of a son?
[TAKUGEN]
Yes.
Seems he crossed the Kiso River
to steal a glimpse at
the Lady of Mino's visage.
Is this true?
[YOSHITATSU] If so, I've
received no such reports,
my lord.
This leaves us with a problem.
If Nobunaga‐sama fails
to return from Mino,
Owari will search for him
using all their forces
and won't think twice
before crossing the Kiso.
Did you come here on their
behalf to intimidate us?
Yoshitatsu.
You said he journeyed here to
gaze upon my daughter's face?
Where is she?
That's just it.
She appears to
be missing, my lord.
Then find her!
Yes.
What are you doing
in these woods?
Huh?
[NOBUNAGA]
Are you a companion of hers?
Huh?
I managed to stop the bleeding,
but she needs
treatment right away.
Hurry!
[NOBUHIRO]
Hey! The hero returns!
You little...
You realize you had
everyone worried sick?
[NOBUNAGA]
C'mon, it's no big deal.
[KICHOU]
Father?
You're up. And the pain?
Is it severe?
[KICHOU]
Yes.
It hurts in my chest.
I can't describe it,
but I've never experienced
a feeling like
this in all my life.
And we have that
scatter‐brained idiot
from Owari to thank for it.
How very disturbing.
[KICHOU] With the New Year,
Nobunaga‐sama's brother,
Kanjuurou‐sama came of age,
and the name Nobukatsu
was bestowed upon him.
Also, at this time, to keep
Imagawa forces in check,
Nobuhide‐sama constructed
Suemori Castle, east of Nagoya.
Spring arrived, and with it, the
wedding day finally commenced.
[TAKUGEN]
Since it appears
all the necessary
parties are present,
we'll begin the
ceremony of nuptials.
For Oda Kazusa no Suke Nobunaga‐
sama and Kichou‐ dono .
[screams]
What in the...?
What's wrong with him?
That was strange.
Young master!
Please be silent!
Huh? I'm sorry.
It's just, my legs were
starting to fall asleep.
Unbelievable, acting
that way at his wedding.
Maybe marriage will
finally cause him to grow up.
[chuckles]
Let's go.
Right now?
Yes, my lord?
I'm to be killed.
By whom?
By Kichou!
Huh?
You remember the ninja
back on Mount Inaba?
She and the Lady of Mino
are the same!
An assassin!
As far as jokes go,
this is definitely one of
your better ones my lord.
Tsuneoki. I need you to
stay by my side all night.
I'll have to decline.
Why?
I don't know
if this is another joke,
but I'm not sure why
you want me present.
Unless you're
intending to show off
the consummation of
your marriage to me?
Do you understand
what I'm telling you?
I know that you're nervous,
but everybody has a first time.
Good night and best of luck.
[NOBUNAGA]
Wait.
Don't leave me.
Tsuneoki!
It's fine.
As long as I don't
leave an opening,
the Viper's poison won't get me.
And I have this
concealed chamber.
[gasps] How did you...?
I wanted to make sure you
didn't end up catching a cold.
But the lock.
Funny, I didn't notice
a lock on the door.
[gasps]
A trap!
As if she didn't lace this
with a deadly poison!
Oh, Nobunaga?
What're you eating?
This?
Just some delicious food
Kichou prepared for me.
Spit it out!
Right this instant!
Calm down.
I'm sure she wouldn't mind
making you some more.
Well that hit the spot.
[KICHOU chuckles]
Wow, great.
Kichou?
An assassin?
You're not laughing.
The truth is,
this wouldn't be
the first time Kichou‐dono
was married to someone.
[NOBUNAGA gasps]
Do you mean...?
We were careless.
With Nobuhide‐sama
downed by his illness,
the Owari province would be
instantly splintered apart
if you were to be killed.
Even if we were to
eliminate Kichou‐dono
before she has
the chance to strike.
Dousan would then be given
just cause for invading Owari.
Avenging his daughter's death.
Ruthless.
He's not called
"The Viper" just for show.
Why doesn't she
get it over with?
Or, maybe she enjoys
watching me cower,
like a cat that enjoys toying
with a mouse before eating it.
[TAKUGEN]
I'd suggest putting yourself
in her position, my lord.
Who? Kichou?
Once you do,
I suspect the answer will
become clear to you.
[KICHOU]
What is this?
A message. From your father.
He says to finish off Nobunaga.
After that, you can return home.
I understand.
It's just...
I feel a pain in my bosom.
Has your wound
not fully healed yet?
If so, I could kill him for y‐‐
No, Kaede.
It's fine.
Leave it.
Why are you in here?
I felt parched
and needed a drink.
Come on. Let's walk
Is it far?
What do you want to show me?
We're almost there.
You can only see this
when there's a full moon.
It's a special sal tree.
[KICHOU]
Why bring me here?
[NOBUNAGA]
It has another name.
The Nirvana Tree.
If I'm to die,
I want this to be my last sight.
[KICHOU]
As you wish.
But I won't go quietly.
If I die tonight,
Takugen will share the
circumstances of my demise.
Using my death
as a rallying cry,
the Oda will unite and likely
call for Mino's destruction.
[NOBUNAGA]
Stop!
[KICHOU]
If I don't fulfill my mission.
It's over, and I can never
return home to my father.
Kill me.
If you died, it would
only cause more problems.
Are you that afraid of it?
Stirring up trouble with Mino?
[NOBUNAGA grunts]
That's not what I
was talking about!
Damn it!
You don't think I understand how
much you look up to your father?
But what about you?
How much thought has
he given his daughter?
Here you are, plying your trade
while carrying these scars.
Does he care
what happens to you?
You said you
can't return to him.
[NOBUNAGA]
Then stay here by my side.
Imagine if word got out
my bride left me.
Do you know how
terrible that'd look?
People would think I was awful.
[DOUSAN]
What?
And he still took her in?
Yes.
I never could have imagined
he'd willingly accept
poison from the Viper.
So, they call him Nobunaga, huh?
Very amusing.