[KICHOU]
Hidetaka‐sama.
You left this life immersed
in the joy of love.
Was that perhaps
a form of good fortune?
[KICHOU] After all,
you never knew the suffering
and sadness that
eventually comes.
Be glad, one and all!
Nobukatsu‐ sama has
resolved to lead the Oda clan!
[RETAINER A]
Oh! A fine decision, my lord.
[RETAINER B] We were waiting
for this day to arrive!
Obviously, we're overjoyed.
Nobukatsu‐ sama possesses
the right temperament needed
to succeed Nobuhide‐ sama .
From this day forth,
he'll boldly name
himself head of the clan
and work toward
ousting Nobunaga‐ sama .
Finally, we'll be rid
of your brother
and all his ridiculous whims.
Indeed, with your help.
[RETAINERS]
Yes, sir!
[KATSUIE] This is
Nobunaga‐ sama 's territory.
If Nobukatsu‐sama occupies it,
that would send a message,
loud and clear.
We'll replace the leadership
with our own subordinates.
Even if warfare breaks out,
we must continue to keep
our lord's name untainted.
[TSUZUKI]
Too indulgent.
We can't be selective
about our methods.
We should use coin
to amass supporters
and allow them to loot, kidnap,
whatever else they choose.
But what are you saying?
Then Nobukatsu‐ sama 's
reputation
would be that of a ruffian!
In war, fathers may
see their sons die
and sons may watch
their fathers die,
but they must step over
the bodies and press on.
Even the Heike would
have escaped destruction
if they had adopted
the necessary methods.
He's trying this again?
His silver tongue is
the most irritating part.
What's your opinion,
Shibata‐ dono ?
[KATSUIE] It's for
Nobukatsu‐ sama to decide.
For now, we'll begin by blocking
passage on the roadways.
We'll prevent arms and supplies
from being brought into Kiyosu.
Thus isolating them.
I entreat you to grant us
victory on the battlefield.
I entreat you to grant
us victory on the battlefield!
Your hair is so
lustrous and beautiful.
Up to now, you've tried
to maintain purity
in other regards, such as
governance and warfare.
You wanted to keep
to the side of good.
But with those standards,
you'll never be able
to defeat Nobunaga.
You know the truth.
All things that
were pure and good.
Hidetaka‐ sama carried with him
to the Pure Land of Paradise.
They no longer
exist in this world.
I am aware.
If Nobunaga is to be destroyed,
we must first become devils.
Tell me, Kurando.
Devils, do they live
in a colorless world?
I don't understand.
[NOBUKATSU] I've never
heard of it happening before,
but since I've sworn
vengeance on Nobunaga.
My vision has changed.
It's a world of nothing
but black and white.
That's truly a
mysterious thing, my lord.
Seems thoroughly devilish,
don't you think?
[laughs]
[TSUZUKI]
That's right.
Become a devil.
Press ahead without
concern for your reputation.
[KICHOU]
On this day,
Tsuzuki proposed the high
ground of Ryuusen Temple,
which was surrounded
by rivers and marshes,
be made the troop headquarters.
Nobukatsu‐ sama left the
overseeing of this arrangement
to his close confidant.
[TAKUGEN]
May I present Otsuru.
She serves as head
of a nearby village.
[NOBUNAGA]
What's this?
Actually, she says
there's a rumor spreading.
The villagers are convinced
that a war is imminent.
Everyone is feeling
a great sense of unease.
Please issue a
proclamation, my lord,
to spare our village
from any troop harassment,
violence, setting fires,
taking our homes.
Hold on, back up.
I've no problem
issuing a proclamation,
but what's this talk
about a war starting?
According to what's being said,
Suemori Castle
is attacking soon.
Nobukatsu?
Why haven't I heard
anything about this?
And who are they
going to fight against?
Imagawa? Saitou?
They're fighting you.
[gasps]
I can assure you
that's not true.
It's only a rumor.
Trust me.
I... I hope so, my lord.
I will issue a proclamation.
Whoever the intended foe is,
I will not permit any plundering
or setting of fires
in my realm.
[OTSURU]
We greatly appreciate it.
[TAKUGEN] I'm not convinced
this is simply a rumor.
There are several reports
that a large number of roads
have been blocked off
by Suemori troops.
Nobukatsu.
It's true.
[TSUNEOKI] We must
prepare ourselves for war.
It doesn't make sense.
Why would he wage war
against his own brother?
I'm going to meet
with him face‐to‐face!
[TSUNEOKI]
You can't, my lord!
Sentimentality isn't
going to help us.
You must deal with betrayal
swiftly and without emotion.
Even if it's my own family?
Of course!
You're lord of Kiyosu Castle,
responsible for a great
many troops and common folk.
And a moment's indecision
would mean the loss
of countless lives.
This is no time to
dwell on heartache!
A decision must be made.
If we're going to protect them,
we need to prepare now!
I heard you, Tsuneoki.
Ready our troops to leave.
It's a beautiful night, my lord.
The moon looks lovely.
I'm sorry, but I wish
to be alone right now.
All right.
[NOBUNAGA]
Nobukatsu.
Why would you do this?
Gazing at the
moon alone, my lady?
[KICHOU]
That explains it.
Poor Nobunaga.
He's in agonizing pain.
[TSUNEOKI] Telling him not
to wallow in his feelings
would be of no use.
Despite being aware of that,
you refuse to hold back
when it is necessary
to tell him hard truths.
Retainers usually
desire to be liked
by whomever they're serving.
But you aren't interested
in flattering him.
You only think of Nobunaga‐ sama
intensely, deeply,
with all your heart.
I'm unable to act that way.
Tell me, how do
I become more like that?
I believe our two situations
are entirely different, my lady.
And yet, they're not!
Even though we both adore him
and are continuously
by his side.
I still don't have
the resolve to tell him.
I was wondering.
This Kitsuno‐sama.
Tell me what kind
of person she is.
[TSUNEOKI] Someone
Nobunaga formerly yearned for.
[KICHOU]
As I thought.
His feelings for her are
a distant memory now.
I know Nobunaga‐ sama ,
and I guarantee he
would never do anything
to hurt you, my lady.
That's what hurts the most.
The kindness he shows.
Here's Nobunaga‐ sama 's
proclamation.
You can all rest easy now.
[OTSURU]
Thank you very much.
[KITSUNO SERVANT B]
You're not serious.
I swear it's true.
[OTSURU] Those are
members of the Ikoma House!
[TOSHIIE]
Oh. It's Kitsuno‐ sama ?
She's come far to do business.
I really hope war isn't
in our near future.
[RUFFIAN]
Is it true they're gonna pay us?
[TSUZUKI RETAINER A]
If you become a foot soldier
for Nobukatsu‐ sama .
And when the war breaks out,
you can do as you wish.
Pillage, burn, take anything
and everything you want!
[RUFFIANS]
Yeah!
Our fate rests upon the
outcome of this one battle!
Destroy Nobunaga!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
Greetings, my lord.
We are your servants to command.
[NOBUKATSU]
Mm.
Where has Tsuzuki‐dono gone?
He's out leading another force.
[gasps]
You'll hand over
all your valuables
and crops this instant!
Defy us and we'll cut you down!
Enough of this!
I'm in charge of this village!
Bring someone who will
understand reason!
You insolent fool.
Quickly, get word
to Nobunaga‐ sama !
Right!
Kitsuno‐sama!
[TOWNSMAN B] I swear there's
nothing of value in my house!
Step aside!
[ATTENDANT]
He says troops from Suemori
have taken over their village!
They what?
Muster the troops!
[TSUNEOKI]
Yes, sir!
What's the meaning of this?
Nobody said anything
about setting fire to the rice
before it was harvested!
You don't win a war
by observing niceties.
Reporting, my lord.
I've added 300
more troops to our army.
Three hundred?
How were you able
to ready that many?
Nobukatsu‐ sama put the
matter directly into my hands.
He what?
It doesn't matter
what methods we use.
Nobunaga needs to be destroyed!
If you want this field,
you'll have to fight us!
Kill them all!
This goes no further!
Why you. Attack him!
[TOSHIIE]
Take this.
[NOBUKATSU SOLDIER J]
It's him!
Withdraw!
[TSUNEOKI] This is
Nobunaga‐ sama 's dominion!
Don't stand there!
Take his head!
If you won't retreat,
we'll cut you down!
[KICHOU] Nobunaga‐ sama 's
force was roughly 700 troops.
By contrast, Nobukatsu's
numbered 1,700.
This conflict, later referred
to as the "Battle of Inou,"
began with the
lord of Kiyosu Castle
at an overwhelming disadvantage.
[KATSUIE] My reputation is based
on my skill on the battlefield!
This is my way!
Damn it!
We cut them down,
but more keep coming!
[MESSENGER A]
Reporting, my lord!
Our force is dominating!
Hayashi Hidesada‐ dono
and Michitomo‐ dono
are driving the enemy back!
[RETAINER C]
All right!
Elder Brother!
No holding anything back!
Agreed!
Nobunaga!
Where are you?
Stand your ground!
The enemy's comprised
of traitors and sell swords!
They'll break rank quickly!
We fight on the side of justice!
Got him! Let's finish him!
[TSUNEOKI]
This is for Nobunaga‐sama!
Burn it into your hearts!
If you do, without fail,
we'll win!
[SASSA]
For Nobunaga‐sama!
[MURAI]
Victory!
Nobunaga!
How long I've waited for the
opportunity to cut you down!
Michitomo! But why?
You're such a fool!
There's no way we would
leave Owari to the likes of you!
Never!
[NOBUNAGA]
Cast it aside.
Cast aside sentiment!
Cast aside dependency!
Hold fast! Stand your ground!
Michitomo!
His army's truly fearsome.
We've only viewed him
as a scatterbrained fool,
but is it possible
Nobunaga‐ sama is idolized
this much by all his followers?
Against such mighty bonds,
numbers alone
cannot determine victory.
[KICHOU] How can
Nobukatsu‐ sama not see
what's in his brother's heart?
Where are you?
Kitsuno‐sama!
[KICHOU]
What happened to her?
She got separated
from us somehow.
What is she wearing?
A deep‐red obi sash and‐‐
I've got it.
Let me go!
Stop this!
If you don't, I'll...
Ha! You should've
brought a larger blade.
[OTSURU]
Are you all right?
Kitsuno‐sama?
You're safe!
I'm so glad!
We're forever grateful.
I never thought we'd
find ourselves in a battle.
[KICHOU]
Leave the village at once.
Do you know the way?
Yes.
If you would. Please.
Do all you can to
protect Nobunaga‐ sama !
Promise me you'll do your best.
Yes.
Even at the cost of my life.
[KICHOU]
So that's who she is.
Strong, in a dignified way.
[MESSENGER B]
Reporting, my lord!
Michitomo‐dono is slain!
And Hidesada‐ dono has
fled from the battlefield!
Reporting, my lord!
Our army has been routed!
That can't be!
I will go myself!
We should turn around!
Keep moving forward!
Glad to see you,
Nobukatsu‐ sama !
What happened to the troops?
A great many have fled,
starting with the foot soldiers!
Money can buy you men,
but never buy their loyalty!
Soldiers without
resolve are useless!
Only a small number
will stand by my side.
So this is the reality.
[laughs]
Leave this for me
to take care of, my lord!
Ride to the safety
of Suemori Castle!
Where are you going?
[TSUZUKI]
Fighting a lost battle?
Idiotic!
Nobunaga‐sama!
It's your brother!
Nobukatsu!
Tell me!
Why are we enemies?
Why must you and I fight?
[TSUNEOKI]
Nobunaga‐sama!
[roars]
That's far enough!
[MURAI]
Seize him!
[KICHOU] Nobunaga‐ sama 's
army was victorious
due to its resolve and unity.
Nobukatsu‐ sama ended up being
confined to Suemori Castle.
[KATSUIE]
Nobukatsu‐sama!
You mustn't!
[NOBUKATSU]
Release me, Shibata.
[KATSUIE]
You'd leave us retainers behind?
I won't let you!
[GOZEN]
I beg you!
Please, let his
sentence be lenient!
Imagine if Nobuhide‐ sama
and Hidetaka were here!
Surely, they would
have asked you the same!
Nobunaga.
Be merciful!
This is a mother's
desperate plea!
[TAKIGAWA] Nobukatsu‐ dono
deserves a harsh punishment.
And his retainers should be
given the same treatment!
We can't allow traitors
to be pardoned!
[KICHOU] Nobunaga‐ sama was
pressed to make a hard decision.
[NOBUNAGA] There are a host
of things I'd like to ask.
But what's done can
never be taken back.
Many men were sacrificed
in the battle, on both sides.
I never want to war
with my own family again.
You understand,
don't you, Nobukatsu?
Yes.
All will be just as you say.
[NOBUNAGA] The whole time, he
never once looked me in the eye.
You should have executed him.
Letting him live,
it's too lenient.
[NOBUNAGA]
I realize that,
but I'm unable to leave
my feelings behind.
Please, forgive me
this one time!
I make this solemn
promise to you.
This will be my only betrayal!
I beg you!
[KICHOU] Nobukatsu‐ sama
had his crimes forgiven,
and it was thought
stability would return.
However.
[NOBUKATSU] Not only did
I endure unbearable shame,
now he's forcing me to
stay alive and wallow in it!
[TSUZUKI] I know you're in pain,
but it's all right, my lord.
All you have
to do is stay alive.
Then you'll have the
opportunity you need.