Maintain focus!
Concentrate
Yes, you're right.
[KATSUIE] The arrow will
invariably find its target
if your perception
remains unclouded,
as clear as a mirror,
still as water!
I think I've found the
source of my distraction.
It's you.
[KATSUIE sighs]
Sorry.
[ATTENDANT A]
Hey, it went that way!
I see it!
[NOBUKATSU]
What is going on over there?
Sorry! The bird got
loose somehow!
Bird?
[ATTENDANT B] Quick! Hold
it down before it gets away!
[ATTENDANT A]
It's heading right for you!
[gasps]
[ATTENDANT B]
Who is that guy?
Are you injured, my lord?
Um, no.
Thank you.
May I please know the name
of the man who saved me?
Kurando.
You may call me Tsuzuki Kurando.
[KICHOU]
Oda Nobunaga.
When the world was at war,
he eclipsed it like a demon god.
Though much has
been written about him,
the man I knew
differed from the legend.
Tonight, let me tell you
a bit more about
who that Nobunaga‐sama
really was.
[NOBUNAGA] Apparently it
got sent to Nobukatsu's place
instead of being
delivered here.
As noted in this
letter of complaint.
Back up one moment.
What is this
mystifying creature?
Furthermore, why was it
supposed to be delivered here?
If I'm being completely honest,
it wasn't my
first choice for a pet.
I couldn't get
my hands on a peacock,
but you can have
this creature instead!
You could have told him no.
It's a rare species.
Whatever it is,
it won't stop staring.
I'm wondering, what sort
of bird is this anyway?
Something like...
It's an ostrich!
Well, I know it's male.
It's a real shame it won't
be able to lay any eggs.
No chicks, unfortunately.
Are you disappointed?
Actually,
I was just thinking about
how many rolled omelets
we could have made!
[NOBUNAGA] I understand
being annoyed with the mix up,
but Nobukatsu should've come
here and complained directly.
That's not feasible
given his new position
as master of Suemori Castle.
He can't get away as easily now.
Well, You would think he could
make an exception in my case.
We are brothers.
Yeah, but...
...the only reason
I can think for him to visit
would be a special circumstance.
So you're saying
I'm not special enough.
[TOSHIIE]
Nobunaga‐sama!
Preparations for
making mochi are done!
Wait. I have an idea!
[NOBUMORI]
A New Year's Party?
You betcha!
Nobunaga‐sama's family
will all gather together
in Nagoya Castle
in order to celebrate
the New Year!
And they're going
to have some company.
Can you believe we received
permission to join them?
It's amazing, right?
Ah. Though I was planning
a solitary wilderness retreat
to work on improving
my swordsmanship.
Enough with the austerities.
We ought to attend.
Not like any of us have a home
to go to for New Year's anyway.
One thing is for sure,
I'm definitely showing up.
I mean, we can
probably down saké
to our heart's content so...
Perhaps you should get
your appetite in check,
or we won't have
any food left to go with it.
Oh, there's one
more proclamation.
If you're joining in
the celebrations,
then each of you has to
perform some sort of talent
for the guests!
I'm sorry, what?
Now hold on!
We don't all possess artistic
talent apart from martial arts!
Guys!
This isn't about us!
We're trying to liven up
Nobunaga‐sama's banquet.
Everyone, do your part!
Hah!
[applause]
Show remorse!
Come!
Gather around!
And watch as...
[TSUNEOKI]
I must say, not a bad idea.
It'd be difficult for anyone
to turn down a New
Year's celebration.
That's my brother for you.
Still the same.
What's this about
a banquet, my lord?
[NOBUKATSU] He says that
we have much to discuss,
and we should all get together
when New Year's arrives.
[GOZEN]
You mustn't.
[NOBUKATSU]
Mother!
Nobunaga's actions
have created a rift
with the Principal
Line in Kiyosu.
If we're seen in his company,
it's inevitable we'd come
under their scrutiny as well.
[NOBUKATSU]
There's no need to worry.
It'll be fine.
Nobukatsu!
[KICHOU]
However.
The New Year came,
but no banquet was held.
This was because
Imagawa Yoshimoto,
who had been eyeing
Owari with a hungry stare,
began constructing
a fort at Muraki,
near the neck of
the Chita Peninsula.
If this keeps up.
Mizuno‐dono will be defeated
and Ogawa Castle will fall.
We'll send them aid.
My lord, if we leave the castle,
the Principal Line
will seize the opportunity
and claim it as their own.
I know, but we don't have enough
troops to divide our forces.
[KICHOU] Why don't you
ask my father to help?
Dousan‐dono?
While you travel to Ogawa,
he could defend Nagoya for you.
Let's go with that!
He did what?
How dare he allow
Mino's troops into Nagoya!
He's a complete fool.
Trusting the castle
to a former enemy!
There's simply
nothing more to discuss.
I say we wash our hands of him.
So it's finally come to this.
[TSUNEOKI]
What now, my lord?
There's no choice.
I'll write.
We need to reach out
to my brother
and ask for his assistance.
[KATSUIE]
Nobukatsu‐sama, wait!
Where are you intending to go?
Where?
To aid my brother!
[KATSUIE]
Don't do this, my lord!
His senior retainers
have pulled away.
He's alone without any help.
If I don't go to him,
then who will?
He has Mino's troops and they've
already stationed at Nagoya.
If you were to
leave the castle now,
who's to say they
wouldn't assault Suemori?
Please. Stay.
My brother would never
approve of such an act.
That may be so,
but do you really expect that'll
keep Dousan from trying?
Sir, pardon, but you're
being asked for.
[NOBUKATSU]
What does this concern, Mother?
[GOZEN]
Is it true?
Mino is an occupying force?
Who put these ideas
in your head?
This is your castle.
Nobuhide‐sama
left Suemori to you,
and it's crucial that it
be defended at all costs.
If all we do is keep defending,
eventually it'll fall!
I'd ask that you leave matters
of warfare and strategy to me.
Mother?
I apologize.
Did we wake you?
[HIDETAKA]
Elder Brother!
[NOBUKATSU]
Hidetaka.
[HIDETAKA]
Where are you going?
Nowhere, my child.
In fact, he just made a promise
to never leave.
Isn't that right, Nobukatsu?
[KICHOU]
In the end,
Nobukatsu‐sama
chose not to move.
Nobunaga‐sama left
Nagoya's defenses
in the hands of Dousan
and led his troops out.
They launched an assault
on Muraki Fortress
during an intense storm.
This surprise attack
was a success,
and the Imagawa forces withdrew.
Nobunaga‐sama
had defended Owari.
[NUN] You did not fulfill
the promise you made to us.
Care to explain?
The arrangement we agreed upon
was for you to draw Nobunaga out
and then take control of Nagoya.
We know that, but nobody
could have anticipated
that the Mino forces would
be occupying the castle.
Then perhaps a more direct
approach is what's required.
What?
You don't mean.
Then he's actually
coming to Owari?
There'll be nothing left
after Imagawa‐sama arrives
with one hundred
thousand troops.
Do you wish to survive this?
Then you must perform
a deed to redeem yourselves.
Imagawa has got
some new friends.
Both Takeda of Kai
and Houjou of Sagami.
That hundred thousand
troops, it's no bluff.
Let's hurry.
We don't have any time to waste.
[NOBUNAGA]
Nobukatsu, I hope you are well.
Though we agreed
to meet at New Year's...
Huh?
...the cherry blossoms
are already in full bloom.
Remember the ostrich?
I thought it was male,
but to everyone's surprise,
it ended up laying several eggs.
They're huge, by the way.
The size of a gourd!
The bird wasn't inclined
to incubate them,
so we had several rolled
omelets instead.
They tasted... Well,
you can probably guess.
[TSUNEOKI]
Another letter, my lord?
Tsuneoki.
I've been writing one every day.
So far, no replies.
If you're too persistent,
he may resent you.
Why'd you say that?
[NOBUNAGA]
Nobukatsu, how are things there?
You haven't caught
a cold, right?
I won't say I want
to see your face,
but I'd like a reply, at least.
If you knew how much
I wanted to see you.
I wish we could go
horseback riding together
or gaze up at
the stars and talk.
The way we used to.
If so, then put those feelings
to paper and write back to him.
However close you
both used to be,
it's difficult to
convey feelings
without relying upon
the assistance of words.
Well, look who stopped by.
Takugen Oshou.
Did you have some business
with Nobukatsu‐sama?
Today is Kanbutsu‐e.
As you know.
And seeing as it's the day
of our Lord Buddha's birth.
I was merely paying
a visit in hopes
of asking Nobukatsu‐sama
for a donation.
In the future,
you should follow protocol
and present such
matters to me instead.
[TAKUGEN]
Noted. But we're finished.
My lord.
I'll take my leave now.
Good grief.
That monk's a nuisance.
[TSUZUKI]
Nobukatsu‐sama.
I've picked some flowers
for Kanbutsu‐e, my lord.
Would you put them in that vase?
Is that a toy?
A ball.
It's an old birthday gift
from my elder brother.
Please, tell me more.
Thank you for my present!
I'm the one who
should be thanking you.
[NOBUKATSU]
Hmm?
The morning you were born
and I heard you crying;
I remember being so happy.
Thanks for being my brother.
This is to express my gratitude.
It's more than just a toy.
For me, this is a symbol
of the bond we share.
I don't mean to intrude, my
lord, but I just had a thought.
Why not show how you feel
by giving something back
to your brother?
Huh?
Perhaps a gift for
his upcoming birthday.
Something he can treasure.
It'd express how you feel.
Maybe even better than words.
You think so?
You're right!
Tsuzuki.
Thank you so much.
Is he crying?
A letter from
Nobukatsu‐sama arrived.
Those are tears of pure joy.
And what if he wrote that
he's breaking off contact?
Don't ruin this moment!
Great! Now I'm too afraid
to open it and see what it says!
Kichou!
You read it for me!
It's your letter.
I'm begging you!
[KICHOU]
"Dear elder brother.
Spring has arrived and the wind
feels pleasant upon one's face.
How have you been?"
You can skip past
the introduction
and get to the important part.
"It's nearly here.
The day you were born
is swiftly approaching."
To celebrate, I'd like
to give you a present.
Write back if there's
something you wish for.
See? I told you, Tsuneoki.
I'm glad his response
pleases you, my lord.
[KICHOU]
How shall you answer, my lord?
[sighs]
Say there's no need
to buy me anything,
because the only present that
I want is to see his face again.
[KICHOU]
Sadly.
Nobunaga‐sama's wish
would remain unfulfilled.
[TSUNEOKI]
Presenting.
Shiba Yoshikane‐sama,
Son of Shiba Yoshimune.
Lord protector of Owari.
Treat his wounds immediately!
[RETAINER A]
Sir!
Tell me, what on earth happened?
Sakai Daizen has been in
communication with Imagawa.
It's true.
My father rebuked him,
and Sakai balked.
Quick question.
Who's his father?
Shiba Yoshimune‐sama.
He holds the
highest rank in Owari.
Oh. I see.
He's Lord Protector of Owari,
while the Principal Line
stood as his proxy.
But it's clear Nobutomo‐sama
isn't a man you can depend upon.
The one holding the reins is
his representative, Sakai Daizen
What you're saying is
this Sakai guy's a traitor!
We won't let this stand!
We're ready to
treat his injuries now!
[YOSHIKANE]
I can stand on my own!
There's no way around it!
We have to give
that Sakai bastard
his just desserts, my lord!
[chatter]
What's our course?
[MORISHIGE]
Nobunaga‐sama!
There's trouble!
I know you're harboring
Shiba Yoshikane‐sama
behind your castle walls!
We demand you hand him over!
How about we start
with your names?
Sakai Kounosuke.
I'm retainer to
Oda Nobutomo‐sama!
Lord Protector of Owari!
[TAKIGAWA]
Should I fire?
No. Hold off.
If you refuse to
hand him over to us,
then we'll have
to take him by force!
I've heardd enough
demands out of you!
Toshiie, don't!
[CAVALRYMAN B]
Withdraw!
Yeah, run back to the
hole you crawled out of!
[NOBUNAGA] I guess it's up
to me to protect this baby bird
that's flown into my care,
and fend off the sparks
that are about to fly.
Fine.
Sound the horns!
Prepare to ride out!
[TOSHIIE]
Reporting, sir!
Kiyosu's defenses are
stronger than we thought.
We can't break through them.
Look here.
Imagawa fletching.
That bastard, Sakai.
He must have allied with them.
If so, I think it's safe to
assume they have stockpiles
of weapons and provisions
in preparation for a siege.
They planned for this to happen.
[DAIZEN]
Hmph!
Send them a volley,
like Nobunaga tried.
My powder's damp!
Not today!
I owe you one!
Hey, don't worry about it.
They're planning
to attack the rear gate!
Another volley!
[SAKAI RETAINER]
Nobunaga's troops have circled
around the East Gate.
We have to stop!
It's madness for the Oda clan
to be killing its own line!
There's no turning back
for us at this point.
So do me a favor, Tono‐sama,
quit your complaining!
Send out a sortie!
[RETAINER C] The bottom line
is we need more men.
As things stand,
we can't breach their defenses.
[TSUNEOKI]
What shall we do?
My brother asks that
we send reinforcements.
It was treasonous to attack
the Shiba, the Lord Protectors,
but to defy the Principal Line!
He's your brother.
And the moment has
finally arrived for you
to reciprocate the same
love he's shown you.
I believe you're right, Tsuzuki.
Prepare to ride!
[GOZEN]
I won't allow it!
Mother.
Siding with Nobunaga means
defying those who're above us.
It'll bring nothing but
disaster to our house.
Any word from Nobukatsu?
Nothing yet, my lord.
You can't stay!
Leave the rearguard
to me and retreat!
So this is how it ends.
[horn sounds]
You... You made it!
Nobukatsu!
[NOBUKATSU]
Charge!
[GOZEN]
Why are you so determined to go?
[NOBUKATSU]
To defend my elder brother.
To protect all of Owari,
including you, Mother.
Thank you for this gift.
All right!
Counterattack!
Stand firm and fight!
[SAKAI SOLDIER C]
Kawajiri‐dono has been slain!
I won't forget this, Nobunaga!
[NOBUNAGA]
Nobukatsu!
[GOZEN] Very well,
but I have one condition.
You are not to dismount
your horse for any reason.
Return home to
your mother, unharmed.
That is your sole duty.
Tell me one thing.
Just what did my brother ever do
to make you
despise him so greatly?
Sadly, that's not
something for you to know.
Sir. Let's ride home.
Gozen‐sama awaits your return.
I'm well aware.
It's dusk, after all.
Perhaps he wasn't able
to make out your face
from atop the hill.
Let's call him back.
No. Don't.
The fact he showed up is enough.
[KICHOU]
And thus, the conflict ended.
Oda Nobutomo took
responsibility for the uprising
and committed seppuku.
Oda Nobunaga‐sama
acquired Kiyosu Castle
and made it his
new command post.
[NOBUKATSU]
Did I manage to pay you back?
Or at the very least,
show how thankful I am for you?
[TSUZUKI]
There you are, my lord.
Tsuzuki?
I see you're busy reliving
old memories again.
No, I... I was just...
I sense your loneliness.
Let me cure you of it.
Are you hurt?
[sighs]
Nobunaga‐sama.