[gasps]
[GOZEN]
Come now, Hidetaka!
Could you at least try to keep
your robes from getting dirty?
Sorry, Mother,
but he's in his own world
and can't hear anyone else.
Hidetaka‐sama has
a deep appreciation
for all manner of insects.
[GOZEN]
He's not like normal children.
I wish for him to
live quietly somewhere,
away from the strictures
of a samurai family.
[NOBUKATSU]
You can put your mind at ease.
As long as he lives,
I'll protect him from any harm.
I trust you will.
[NOBUKATSU]
Hidetaka.
Show me your latest discovery.
Sure. Look at this!
[GOZEN]
Huh? Is that true?
Yes, during the recent battle.
Nobukatsu‐sama dismounted
and charged the enemy.
And even came close to
losing his life in the process.
That's horrifying,
and after I told him not
to leave his horse's saddle.
I beg you, my lady,
do not reproach him.
His only concern
was helping the one
who inherited control
over the family.
He's blameless.
Nobunaga.
Fool. He's selfish.
And one day he'll ruin us.
Though he holds power.
I don't want him in our lives.
That would be hard
to pull off, at least,
as long as the bonds
of brotherhood hold.
Luckily.
I have a stratagem in mind.
[GOZEN]
A stratagem?
I hate to think how
things would've turned out
if Nobukatsu hadn't shown up.
Yes, my guts were
churning with fear.
[NOBUNAGA] It looked like he had
something he wanted to tell me.
The way things stand now,
he can't appear
overly familiar with you.
I only wish that he
would speak his mind.
[TSUNEOKI]
We've arrived, my lord.
This is Ikoma estate.
[NOBUNAGA]
Kitsuno‐dono.
Thank you again for
your help the other day.
How have you been since
we last ran into each other?
I've been keeping busy.
With so many
guests to take care of,
there's hardly any free time.
Seems the estate has changed.
I hear it's become a place
for cultural exchange,
frequented by
foreign traders and monks.
[KITSUNO]
Yes.
Many people deepen their
cultural understanding here
by exchanging information
about different countries
and business practices.
[NOBUNAGA gasps]
This is unbelievable!
Nobunaga‐sama.
I'll introduce
you around, my lord.
[NOBUNAGA] I got a thank‐you
gift for Nobukatsu too.
Everything worked out!
I hope he's pleased by it.
Please don't tell me
you're thinking of
delivering his gift in person.
You mean I can't?
[TSUNEOKI]
Of course not.
[sighs]
I'll serve as a messenger
and will communicate
your feelings clearly to him.
Sounds perfect!
Please do that!
[HIDETAKA RETAINER A]
It's too dangerous, my lord!
[HIDETAKA RETAINER B]
Hidetaka‐sama!
I'm just fine!
Who is this Hidetaka‐sama?
Nobunaga‐sama's
younger brother.
I got one! Look!
Are you okay, Hidetaka‐sama?
I see you found
a diving beetle larva.
Insects fascinate you as well?
I used to play with them a lot.
This season you can find
dragonfly nymphs
and water fireflies.
[gasps]
[HIDETAKA]
Say.
Sometime soon
let's watch the fireflies!
If you'd like.
Of course. Sounds fun.
Until then.
And that's a promise!
There's something
about Hidetaka‐sama.
Almost soothing.
[NOBUKATSU] If only we could
speak heart‐to‐heart one time.
Thank my brother
for these rare goods.
I appreciate the gifts.
[TSUNEOKI]
I will.
Additionally, I have a proposal
that I wish to put forward.
What would you say to holding an
audience with Nobunaga‐ sama ?
He believes this would allow
for a more candid exchange.
To be perfectly honest. I was‐‐
[TSUZUKI] You put my lord
in a difficult position.
Nobunaga‐sama has left us
with serious doubts
concerning his leadership.
[TSUNEOKI]
And what does that mean?
Need I cite multiple examples
of your lord's selfish behavior?
We find it incomprehensible
and are concerned about
the Oda clan's future.
You're what?
Tsuzuki‐dono!
How dare you
interrupt like that?
Tsuzuki, that was rude.
I feel I've spoken too
forwardly with you.
I apologize for that,
Ikeda‐dono.
He hasn't been with us long
and still hasn't gotten a
grasp of how things work.
To be clear, we don't share
his feelings in any way.
Tsuneoki‐dono.
We have treated
you rudely today.
[TSUNEOKI]
No.
If Nobunaga‐sama were here,
he'd most likely laugh it off.
He's a person who never tries
to fetter what's in our hearts.
Retainers or otherwise.
[TOSHIIE] What was that piece
of filth Tsuzuki's problem?
Next time I'll kill
him on the spot.
Seriously though,
what a complete idiot.
Shooting his mouth off like
that without even thinking.
Actually, I suspect
it was calculated.
[TOSHIIE]
Hmm?
Like deliberately tossing
a stone into still waters.
No doubt there was
some motive behind it.
Tsuzuki, what on earth
were you thinking?
I was only stating
the shared opinion
on behalf of everyone else.
And just as others have
judged the current situation,
I also find it dangerous.
Nobunaga‐sama controls us.
Ah! Not you too?
I don't want to
lead over the clan!
My brother inherited that role,
and it's what
my father wished for.
And yet Nobunaga‐sama couldn't
even be bothered to show up
for Nobuhide‐ sama 's funeral.
That's not all.
He let Mino troops
into his castle,
and there was the
Muraki conflict.
His thought process isn't clear.
That much is obvious.
We can't rely on him.
[GOZEN]
I'm in agreement.
Nobunaga is a
wellspring of troubles.
I have no doubt one day
he'll bring great misfortune
upon the Oda clan.
Mother?
I daresay, I am of the
same opinion as Gozen‐sama
[RETAINER A]
As am I!
And me too!
[discussion continues]
You're troubled.
Get out of here.
I feel surrounded.
Everybody's raising me up,
trying to manipulate me.
It's as if I no longer
have any freedom.
The more Nobunaga
behaves as he chooses,
the more trapped
you will become.
Please make things
easier on yourself
and unbind these fetters
that hold you down.
Your hair's a mess.
It's not a good look for you.
[KICHOU] At the same time,
there were turbulent shifts
surrounding leadership
within Mino.
Yoshitatsu had
inherited control of the clan,
but his disgruntled younger
brothers began planning
to oust him by raising up
the now‐retired Dousan.
[KAEDE] Large upheavals
will likely come to Mino soon.
That has an ominous ring to it.
My elder brother Yoshitatsu
is cunning, resourceful,
and ruthless.
Nobunaga‐sama.
The question is what will
Dousan‐dono's move be?
Still, though,
we should prepare.
[ATTENDANT] Excuse me, my lord,
Hidetaka‐ sama is here.
[NOBUNAGA]
Hm?
Uh, wait. My little brother?
How unusual for Hidetaka to
come all this way to visit us.
I haven't seen him in ages.
[TSUNEOKI] Oh! They look
lively, swimming around!
Yeah, they do!
Oh. It seems the fireflies
haven't emerged yet.
But when they do,
I'll be sure to tell you!
And I'll be looking
forward to it.
[chuckles]
It appears he and Tsuneoki
have a great deal in common.
He knows I'm his brother, right?
Hidetaka‐sama,
stay right there.
Don't move.
[HIDETAKA]
A grasshopper?
Was it perched
on top of my head?
It was and looking
quite comfortable.
[laughs]
That reminds me.
From what I understand,
you've become a familiar face
over at the
Ikoma estate recently.
Huh? Oh.
Right.
Then I suppose you've
already heard the news
about her remarrying.
Huh? That's hard to believe.
She only recently
lost her husband.
[OHANA] He's apparently
a rich man from Sakai.
He took pity on Kitsuno‐dono
and introduced
himself as a suitor.
[KICHOU]
1555.
Saitou Yoshitatsu,
Lord of Inabayama Castle,
murdered his
younger brothers,
purging the family of
any chance of divisions.
[KAEDE] You realize this puts
you in a perilous situation.
A rift is likely between the
Oda and the Saitou of Mino.
If so, your value
as a wife will be gone,
and your life may be in danger.
Dissolve the marriage
and come away with me.
Kaede, I...
Is it true
Dousan‐ dono 's fled?
Yes.
My lord is in Sagiyama Castle.
I never imagined Yoshitatsu
would make his move so quickly.
I miscalculated, damn!
We can no longer
consider Mino our ally.
We'll supply
Dousan‐dono troops.
And you'll guide them.
As things stand,
you're less a protector to
him and more of a burden.
[gasps]
[MICHITOMO] Has Nobukatsu‐ sama
still not made a decision?
With Dousan no longer a threat,
we can make allies more easily
and take control
from Nobunaga‐ sama .
He could try to hold
on to his position
by claiming he belongs
to the Principal Line.
Why are you taking the
longest route to the goal?
You realize there are swifter,
more direct methods
of eliminating him.
What you're proposing is...
it's far too drastic!
That would besmirch
Nobukatsu‐sama's good name.
[KATSUIE]
Hmmm...
That ambitious upstart.
His recent words and
deeds go beyond the pale.
He's been currying favor
with Nobukatsu‐ sama
and Gozen‐ sama .
He's shrewd, I'll give him that.
[NOBUKATSU]
I really do want to speak
with my elder brother just once.
But considering how
sensitive the situation is.
Even getting a letter to him
is next to impossible.
[HIDETAKA RETAINER A]
Is that so, my lord?
[HIDETAKA]
I swear!
I'm not making it up.
Careful, brother.
You mustn't touch it.
Right, I'm sorry!
I'm planning on taking it over
to show Ikeda
Tsuneoki‐ dono pretty soon.
[NOBUKATSU]
Funny you should mention that.
I hear you two have
become close recently.
Is something wrong with that?
[NOBUKATSU]
No.
Of course not.
Actually, there's a favor
I'd like to ask of you.
Whenever you meet with him
next, bring this with you,
and pass it to Nobunaga.
A letter?
Yes.
Can I trust you with this task?
I understand.
Here.
All right.
I'll leave tomorrow
to deliver it.
[TSUZUKI]
So, you're having Hidetaka
become your connective link.
I see.
Both of his retainers are
old men, removed from politics.
None of them would pry.
Quite a brilliant
plan, actually.
You thought this through.
I should have figured you
would be opposed to this too.
Quite the opposite, my lord.
I have no desire
to intrude any further
into your precious
brotherly ties.
You're free to do as you wish.
While it may not seem like it,
my only concern is
for your happiness.
Nothing else matters.
[TSUZUKI]
Brotherly ties.
Who needs them?
A nuisance.
Where are you going?
I won't be long!
You can't enter
the hunting grounds!
Wait!
[HIDETAKA]
They've begun emerging!
I have to let him know!
You mustn't go into
the woods, my lord!
[HIDETAKA]
Tsuneoki‐dono.
[HIDETAKA RETAINER B, A]
Hidetaka‐sama!
[NOBUTSUGU RETAINER]
Terrible news, sir!
[NOBUTSUGU]
What is it?
[NOBUTSUGU RETAINER] It appears
one of the arrows pierced
someone who strayed
onto the hunting grounds!
[NOBUTSUGU]
Are you serious?
Who's the halfwit that wandered
in and got himself shot?
[NOBUTSUGU RETAINER]
Your nephew.
[gasps]
[GOZEN]
Hidetaka!
[sobs] Why?
Not my boy!
Hidetaka!
This isn't happening.
Look at him.
Look at your
brother's face, Nobukatsu.
It's still the same
as it ever was,
as though he's only dreaming.
Why would this happen?
Having my son taken away.
[sobs]
Take my mother
to her bedchamber.
What is that?
It looks like a letter.
I'll hold onto it.
Hit by a stray arrow
on the hunting grounds.
Truly heartbreaking.
You two were supposed
to protect him!
[HIDETAKA RETAINER B]
Our humblest apologies!
The arrow belonged to one of
Nobutsugu‐sama's retainers!
So why has there been
absolutely no word from him?
[HIDETAKA RETAINER A]
He fled from the spot
as soon as he heard.
[MICHITOMO]
The coward.
[NOBUKATSU]
If only I hadn't sent him
with that accursed letter!
Hidetaka.
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who killed you.
[TSUZUKI] We both know
it wasn't your fault.
It's not my place to say.
But the truth is,
earlier I heard something
troubling, my lord.
Apparently Nobunaga‐sama
refused to receive the letter
your younger brother
was carrying.
He said it defied logic that
you'd entrust Hidetaka‐ sama
with important correspondence
and that you should
have delivered it yourself.
He wouldn't.
Your brother froze, worried
that he would disappoint you.
And then, that's when
the arrow was fired.
If Nobunaga‐sama had accepted
the letter from your brother,
this could have been prevented.
This cannot be merely
written off as a tragic event.
Your older brother is the
source of our misfortunes.
He treats the fate of
the Oda clan as a trifle!
No! That's a lie!
He would never do such a thing!
[KATSUIE]
Nobukatsu‐sama!
We found your brother's killer!
[HIDETAKA RETAINER B]
Death to Nobutsugu‐dono!
[HIDETAKA RETAINER A]
Let us take revenge!
[RETAINER B]
Nobukatsu‐sama!
[chatter continues]
Make your decision.
Begin rallying a force!
Such a piteous fate.
That poor child. He...
Ill fortune is all
that it can be called.
[ATTENDANT]
Nobunaga‐sama!
An emergency messenger has
arrived from Suemori Castle!
[NOBUNAGA] Nobukatsu is going
to take vengeance on our uncle.
He wants reinforcements.
[ALL gasp]
A battle only for revenge.
What will you do?
Will you send troops?
I'm devastated,
same as my brother.
Unfortunately, Hidetaka
had a lapse in judgement
and voluntarily entered
the hunting grounds.
What should I do?
Nobunaga.
If you raise an army,
it must be for a great cause.
Those who wage war
without one will fall into ruin.
Engrave this truth
upon your heart.
[NOBUNAGA]
They're two different things.
Honoring the memory of
my brother and raising an army.
Has my elder brother arrived?
[HIDETAKA RETAINER B]
No, my lord!
It would appear Nobunaga‐sama
is intent on betraying
you once again.
Seems as though
his priorities lie elsewhere.
You left us.
Your family.
What about our
innocent brother's murder?
Do you care nothing about him?
It's like father's
funeral all over again.
When I need you by my side,
you're never there.
[NOBUKATSU] What matters
most to you, elder brother?
Because I have no idea anymore.
Only one thing is clear.
You cannot rely on him.
He will never change.
That's just the way he is.
Knowing this,
will you still cling to
brotherly ties, my lord?
I will never again
call you my brother.
Nobunaga!
[TSUNEOKI] Frolic and play
as much as you'd like,
Hidetaka‐sama.