[TOSHIIE] Looks like
you've lost some weight
since I saw you last.
I hope they're
feeding you enough.
[TOSHIIE]
I know, I know.
I wish I could spend
more time with you, too.
Maeda‐sama!
You've moved up in the world.
There's no reason for you have
to visit the stables anymore.
Oh, it's got nothing
to do with status.
I just can't relax
unless I see their faces.
[PAGE] This raises problems,
Yoshikane‐ sama !
[YOSHIKANE]
Silence!
I'm going falconing!
Bring out a horse!
Was I not clear?
Bring me a horse!
Um, the thing is...
I'm afraid we can't spare
any since Nobunaga‐ sama
is in the middle of a war,
battling the Isa no Kami.
I see several horses here.
Surely you can spare one.
We cannot.
Why you...!
Just who do you think
you're addressing?
I'm Shiba Yoshikane.
Owari's Lord Protector!
I'm fully aware of
your name and title
and don't need to be reminded.
I'm sorry, but we
can't lend you any.
That's that.
A horse might be required
at a moment's notice, my lord.
You miscreant.
[gasps]
Please hold, my lord.
Ikeda‐dono!
[YOSHIKANE] For this
ill‐mannered lout to talk
this way to the Lord Protector
of Owari is unforgivable!
[TSUNEOKI] It's just as
you say, Yoshikane‐ sama .
He's ill mannered.
Toshiie, cut open
your stomach immediately.
To make amends for his insult,
he shall commit seppuku.
As for the beheading,
the honor is yours.
If Yoshikane‐ sama ,
the esteemed leader
of the Shiba Buei clan,
agrees to perform the
role of kaishaku for him.
Then surely this man
will agree to kill himself.
Understood.
I'm prepared.
Are you ready, Yoshikane‐sama?
[YOSHIKANE]
Enough of this.
You may deal with this
miscreant however you wish.
[sighs]
What's the story with that guy?
We both know the fate of
Yoshikane‐ sama 's father,
and how Nobunaga‐ sama
took vengeance on the killer.
Sure, which is how that devil
came to be under his protection.
It may be true
that the Shiba clan
are Owari's Lord
Protectors by name,
but the one holding real
authority is Nobunaga‐ sama .
In other words, Yoshikane
has a pretty meaningless title.
While it's a nuisance,
so far it's been limited
to the occasional diversion.
Well, he sure likes
making trouble for us.
Also, since we're
on the subject,
if he had agreed to
perform kaishaku for me,
what exactly would
you have done?
If one man's life
puts the issue to rest,
I'd call that a bargain.
[chuckles]
You really are
the worst, Tsuneoki.
[BOTH laugh]
[KICHOU] In the year 1559,
as chastisement
for plotting an uprising
against Nobunaga‐ sama ,
he and Nobukiyo‐ sama attacked
the Oda Ise no Kami clan.
Forcing them to
relinquish Iwakura Castle.
And that's what people mean
when they say he fights
like a demon god!
Naturally, Nobunaga‐ sama
would be the one to unify Owari.
It looks like we'll finally be
able to sleep easier at night!
You've been having trouble
sleeping up till now?
[NOBUMORI] Heh.
It was just a figure of speech.
I can sleep anytime, anywhere.
[ATTENDANT]
They have arrived.
Congratulations on your victory.
Ah! My lady,
please come join us!
You too, Kitsuno‐sama.
Could you not butt in?
Come on, Toshiie.
[TOSHIIE]
When he called out,
I'd never heard
anything like it.
His voice echoed across
the entire field
and roused our spirits!
Is that true?
Ordinarily his voice
doesn't carry at all.
Elder brother.
Nobukatsu?
Nobukatsu!
[KITSUNO]
Nobunaga‐sama?
[NOBUNAGA]
Huh?
[sighs]
Tonight we drink heartily.
Everyone, drink up!
[RETAINERS]
Yeah!
Nobunaga‐ sama doesn't
usually drink this much!
Tonight must be
a special occasion!
If my lord commands it,
I'll obey.
Something the matter?
All of that good cheer
you're seeing is only a front.
Huh?
[TSUNEOKI] He's still grieving
the loss of Nobukatsu‐ sama .
It weighs heavily on him.
What's the story with that monk?
He belongs to the Douboushuu.
Practitioners of various arts.
Tea ceremony,
flower arranging, et cetera.
In other words,
they smell out money
and try to cozy up
to those who have it.
[NOBUNAGA]
What's this?
An incense burner.
What a truly
remarkable design it has.
It's of Chinese origin.
I was fortunate
enough to acquire it
and wanted to show you.
Since you're an individual
who appreciates beauty.
Please, allow me to
demonstrate how it works.
This variety of incense
is extremely uncommon.
It certainly possesses
an agreeable smell.
I heard a thud.
Is everything...
Nobunaga‐sama!
You filth!
What were you
trying to do to him?
[JUUAMI]
I wasn't doing anything!
What's going on?
[TOSHIIE]
Unhand it!
Are you all right, my lord?
[JUUAMI]
He must've been exhausted!
This incense is known
for relieving tension.
[TOSHIIE]
Stop lying!
Show me what you were
trying to hide in your robe!
I assure you,
I've absolutely no idea
what you're referring to, sir.
Then I'll have to make
you show me by force!
I beg you, stop!
I don't have anything on me!
[TOSHIIE]
Why, you...
What did you do?
[TOSHIIE]
That's the whole truth!
I walked in and saw the monk
attempting
to kill Nobunaga‐ sama !
You were also present when
this occurred, Kazumasu?
I can't explain,
but something felt wrong,
and when I entered the room, I
found Toshiie‐ dono and the monk
already engaged
in a struggle.
We couldn't
investigate the incense
since it was scattered
all over the floor.
Well, Toshiie,
what evidence do you have?
Afterwards, when I
searched the monk's robe,
what I discovered was this.
That's just a hairpin.
Is it possible to kill
a person with one of those?
The Douboushuu are a troupe
of what were originally monks.
They have strong ties to shrines
and temples in every region.
If we don't have evidence he
targeted Nobunaga‐ sama 's life,
it could start trouble.
And we can't afford to make
another enemy currently.
[TOSHIIE]
I must pay the price.
[NOBUNAGA]
You what?
I'll leave and never return.
You'll remain here!
[TOSHIIE] If I'm no
longer in your company,
the Douboushuu won't have any
reason to condemn you, my lord.
His blood's on my hands.
No one else's.
If one man's life puts the issue
to rest, that's a bargain right?
However, should the need arise.
I will come running to
Nobunaga‐ sama 's side!
Toshiie!
It's fine this way.
Until we meet again.
Be well.
[NOBUNAGA]
Kichou left.
Nobukatsu is dead.
Now Toshiie is gone.
I haven't been able
to protect anyone.
[TAKUGEN] As of late, there's
been a great deal of coming
and going of the Douboushuu
between Owari and Mino.
Then you suspect
their activities
are somehow being orchestrated
by Saitou Yoshitatsu?
[TAKUGEN]
No.
His role is merely
that of an intermediary.
The one pulling
the strings seems to be.
Shiba Yoshikane‐sama.
What?
Then this coming and going.
They're exchanging
correspondence.
[TAKUGEN]
Yes.
We need to get our
hands on those letters.
It'll be done.
[YOSHIKANE]
It's absurd!
What on earth does he mean
summoning me to him?
[YOSHIKANE RETAINER] I cannot
even begin to imagine, my lord.
Damn!
His rudeness knows no bounds!
I wish to know
what this is about.
First, you will take a seat.
There's a matter
that concerns us.
[YOSHIKANE]
A matter?
Well, what is it?
It's recently come to our
attention that the Douboushuu
have made trips back and forth,
crossing into Mino.
Mino is watching
Nobunaga‐ sama ,
and its leader is waiting for
an opening to strike him down.
So what of it?
I don't see what any of
this has to do with me.
[TSUNEOKI]
We've intercepted...
...some correspondence.
And it's quite damning.
[YOSHIKANE]
What are you insinuating?
You petitioned
Saitou Yoshitatsu‐ dono
and asked that
Nobunaga‐ sama be murdered.
Attempting to
oblige your request,
Juuami was sent here to
carry out the assassination.
As stated clearly
in this letter.
Toshiie was telling
us the truth.
What have you done?
Have you completely forgotten
it was Nobunaga‐ sama
who avenged your father's death?
Stop!
And you chose to repay
the debt by betraying him?
[NOBUNAGA]
Yoshikane‐dono.
I want to hear you
tell me in your own words.
Did you try to have me killed?
Yes!
What if I did?
What's wrong with that?
I am Lord Protector of Owari!
Release me, you insolent dogs!
Don't you know who I am?
[NOBUNAGA]
Betrayed once again.
[KICHOU] Nobunaga‐ sama , full
of despair, saw only one choice.
He banished Yoshikane‐sama.
Because of this,
the Shiba Buei clan fell apart,
and Nobunaga‐ sama
became Owari's ruler.
Thereafter, a messenger
arrived from the shogunate.
It seemed that the rumor of
Yoshikane‐ sama 's banishment
had reached the nominal
holder of the Shogun title.
Ashikaga Yoshiteru.
[TSUNEOKI] So, you've received
a summons from the shogunate
demanding that
you explain the particulars
regarding why you exiled
the Lord Protector.
While it's a nuisance,
I don't suppose I can ignore it.
Gather them all together.
So, we're taking a trip
to the capital, huh?
I've selected you
all to ride with me.
We're honored, but don't you
want more than seven?
There're dangers, but a
large force is unacceptable.
It might be viewed as taking
arms against the Emperor.
Off we go.
So this is crucian carp sushi.
I know it's
my first time trying it,
but don't you find the
flavor to be slightly odd?
Maybe it's because
we're so close to the capital,
but I greatly prefer
our traditional food.
Thank you very much.
Beware of itinerant monks.
Ah! Tsuneoki‐dono!
We want your opinion on these.
You there!
Who sent you?
Looks like
an assassin from Mino.
How did you suspect
he was going to strike?
I...
[KICHOU]
Thus did Nobunaga‐ sama arrive
at his destination,
the capital, Kyoto.
[MORISHIGE]
So this is the famed Kamo River.
Remarkable bridge too.
There're so many wonders.
And look at the
five‐storied pagoda!
[TSUNEOKI] Remember, we didn't
come all this was to sightsee.
We're not out of danger.
Don't let your guard down.
Now now, Tsuneoki,
it's only natural they'd get
excited by all the new sights.
I mean, just look at
how wide this street is!
[sighs]
You'll never change.
[KICHOU] Nobunaga‐ sama
and company took lodgings
in a temple while
awaiting permission
for an audience with the Shogun.
However, they soon
discovered permission
was not readily granted.
[KATSUIE] To summon someone
and not even grant an audience.
What on earth are they thinking?
A great many people
surround the Shogun.
So many in fact, it would appear
news reaches his ear slowly.
They're making a mockery of him.
How long do
they expect us to wait?
When one is forced into
a position of stagnation,
the body begins
to grow lax as well.
I think I'll go work
on my swordplay.
Same for me.
Shall we practice
alongside them?
What else can we do?
[MINO AGENT A]
Pardon me, sirs!
We arrived after hearing
that Oda Kazusa no Suke‐ dono
was staying here.
[NOBUNAGA] Am I to assume
your presence means the Shogun
will grant an audience with me?
Certainly!
Your request has gone smoothly,
and soon you'll have the
pleasure of meeting him.
It took them long enough.
My thoughts exactly.
Look. I'll hear no
more complaining, all right?
We'll meet with the Shogun,
then head right back to Owari.
Why'd we stop?
What?
It can't be.
You mean even this was a trap?!
Who are you?
Mino's agents?
They're tough, whoever they are!
Guard Nobunaga‐sama!
Was the summons
a trap by Mino too?
Damn it!
Nobunaga‐sama!
He's been pulled away!
Retreat!
It's all we can do
just to hold them back!
‐‐Nobunaga‐sama!
[KATSUIE]
Hold it!
After everything,
it's you, Kich‐‐
You're wrong.
In appearance and in name,
I am not the same person I was.
Is that so?
You may have changed, but will
you return and stay by my side?
I'm yours, your shadow.
If you wish it.
I will.
I'll stay by your side forever.
[TSUNEOKI]
Nobunaga‐sama!
[TSUNEOKI] So the
supposed audience was a ploy.
We'll head back for
Owari early tomorrow.
But first, one question.
[KICHOU]
Yes.
What should I call you?
I'm Baba Reijirou.
Reijirou, is it?
I invite you to join
the Cloaked Guard.
As for your past,
it doesn't matter.
I'd hate to think what
would have happened
if you hadn't shown up.
I have no objections!
There's no doubt
your skills are superb.
How about it?
I accept, my lord.
It doesn't matter
how much he's betrayed,
the people who count
always seem to find a way
of coming back into his life.
[KATSUIE]
Mm.
[TSUNEOKI]
Then again.
That's Nobunaga‐sama.
Reports say the Yamaguchis,
father and son,
committed seppuku,
by order of Imagawa Yoshimoto.
Murdering those
who were obedient to him.
It's truly barbaric.
[NOBUNAGA]
This means one thing.
Imagawa is rousing
himself to action.
[KICHOU] It was at this time,
the greatest test Nobunaga‐ sama
had ever encountered
was about to fall upon him.