[NOBUNAGA] Listen carefully
and heed my words!
Luck is for Heaven to decide!
If they charge, retreat.
If they fall back,
press forward!
And if we're victorious,
history will remember those
of you who fought here today!
I swear, your names
will echo through eternity!
Ride with me!
[SOLDIERS]
Yeah!
[NARRATOR] I've heard a story,
how in the spring of 1560,
at Okehazama Gorge,
Nobunaga‐sama attacked.
And with only a force
of 2,000 elite fighters,
successfully defeated Imagawa
Yoshimoto's force of 45,000.
Don't let these
little fish distract you!
Our target is the head
of Imagawa Yoshimoto!
[NARRATOR] His tactics
were like a raging fire.
Terrifying.
They called him a
demon god, a Hell‐fiend.
But before acquiring
those monikers,
he was someone
completely different.
This evening,
I wish to tell you
a little about him.
The real Nobunaga‐sama.
Who he really was.
[TSUNEOKI]
Kippoushi‐sama!
[yawns]
Good morning, Katsusaburou.
More like afternoon.
[NOBUNAGA]
These shutters do a good job
of keeping out the light.
Uh‐huh. I figured this
place would be a disaster.
[NOBUNAGA]
Look!
It's called a musket.
Takugen showed me a drawing,
so I tried making my own.
You load gunpowder into it,
take aim, then bang!
A metal ball takes
down your enemy!
You mean that
stick does all that?
Impossible.
We have more pressing
matters to attend to.
A foreign barbarians' ship
has arrived at Tsushima.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Let's go see about
that ship, Katsusaburou!
Where're you
headed off to, Brother?]
Just over to Tsushima
to break in some horses.
Please, can I come with you?
[GOZEN]
No, you may not.
What would happen if you
were thrown off while riding?
Maybe when you're older.
I'll be off then.
Goodbye, Mother.
Farewell, my lady.
The boy's keen
on his horse rides.
Do you think he's
too preoccupied
with leisurely activities?
I've no idea what's going
through my son's head,
nor do I particularly
care to find out.
[ROKUROU]
You're late.
Yeah, I overslept.
I thought you
were supposed to be
keeping a close eye on him.
I am!
So, what're you thinking?
Most of the packed goods
have already been hauled off.
Just scraps now.
[NOBUNAGA]
Don't get flustered.
There's our mark.
And... go!
Damn chickens!
You're not injured, are you?
[ROKUROU sighs]
Well, all this cargo's gonna
need to be repacked now.
What do you say
we give you a hand?
For a small fee.
[sighs]
After you've picked it up.
Don't get greedy.
[ROKUROU]
How'd it go?
It couldn't have
gone any better!
They took off
without even noticing
that we skimmed
a little bit off the top.
Beautiful!
Wow! Jackpot!
Look at all the treasure those
barbarians were hoarding!
Make sure it all arrives safely
at Takugen Oshou's temple.
He's affiliated with the Mino,
which means it'll
never be traced to us.
Good thinking.
But still, in order to
move this out of the harbor,
we need to find some way
to sneak past the guardhouse.
I guess that won't work.
If we could conceal it somehow.
And not be suspicious.
We're way ahead of you.
Think this will do?
[TAKICHI]
A barrel coffin?
Brilliant!
No guard'll be curious enough
to wanna take a look
inside one of those.
You have such
clever ideas, my lord.
It's obvious that
your brain was created
differently than
the rest of ours.
Ah, come on.
It's time we left,
Kippoushi‐sama.
You're right.
I'll leave the
heavy‐lifting up to you guys.
[ROKUROU]
Before you go.
[NOBUNAGA]
Hmm?
The only reason we've survived
this long is 'cause of you.
And we'll never forget that.
Something to add
to the collection.
Take it!
I'd say you've become
a veritable chief of pilferers,
Kippoushi‐sama.
I prefer to be called
a gentleman thief!
I'm simply sharing
the massive treasure
my father's accumulated
with those less fortunate.
How generous.
I'm sure the Lord Protector
of Mikawa will appreciate
your charitable works.
Hey, now!
[TSUNEOKI]
You know he'll find out.
Like I've said, it was a
mistake for you to befriend
that sort of crowd
in the first place.
Sounds like you're jealous.
I am not jealous!
My only concern is for
the future of the Oda clan,
which your actions
happen to be jeopardizing!
I'll race you to the castle!
Hey!
[NOBUNAGA] If you win,
I'll give you a prize!
As if you've ever won!
Hyah!
[gasps]
Ha!
You're not hurt, are you?
Only startled, I think.
No, I... It's my fault.
Will you forgive me?
[TSUNEOKI]
Are you all right?
Please.
Allow me to help you
to your feet.
That's very kind of you.
[TSUNEOKI]
I'd like to take her home.
Yeah, please do.
All right, I'll be off then.
[NOBUKATSU]
Whatcha looking at?
Huh?
[shrieks]
Don't sneak up on me like that.
That's such a beautiful stone.
Could you tell me
where you found it?
[NOBUNAGA]
Uh... Where I found it.
Oh, sure.
I'll tell you everything.
As soon as we go downstairs.
I was also kinda
hoping you'd tell me
what you do up
here all day, Brother.
Oh, you know,
reading books, writing,
just boring scholarly
stuff mostly‐‐
[NOBUKATSU]
I don't care if it's boring.
I want to stay up here
and read books with you.
[NOBUNAGA]
Another time!
[NOBUKATSU]
No! Right now!
You have to obey me!
Wait. Careful!
[NOBUKATSU ooos]
How long have
you known about this place?
Do you realize
how amazing this is?
I know but, try to
keep your voice down.
You can have this musket
if you don't tell anyone.
What's a musket?
It's an armament the
foreign barbarians use.
Like a weapon?
Listen, it's extremely important
nobody else discovers this room.
It's a secret that
only the two of us
can know about, understand?
Promise me
you won't tell anyone.
Promise.
[sighs]
That's great!
What a relief!
[GOZEN]
Kanjuurou, you know I'd prefer
if you didn't spend
so much time around him.
[NOBUNAGA]
He was just leaving!
Isn't that right, brother?
Right!
Besides, it's a secret,
so I can't tell!
Eh‐heh...
[GOZEN]
A secret?
Nah. He was kidding!
[GOZEN]
Kippoushi.
He's an innocent.
Don't go infecting him
with your bizarre ideas.
Come along, Kanjuurou.
Yes, Mother!
[NOBUNAGA]
Ikoma‐dono's daughter?
That's right.
They both reside at Koori.
The family operates a
horse‐lending business.
And her name's Kitsuno.
Kitsuno?
She was on her way
home from an errand yesterday
when you nearly trampled her.
Fortunately, it seems like
she only twisted her leg.
Nothing major.
Oh yeah, she also
wanted to apologize
for inconveniencing you.
Is that all she said?
You were expecting more?
Of course not.
[TSUNEOKI]
If I didn't know better,
I'd say she caught your eye.
That's nonsense!
Yeah, you've got that right.
Remember, you are
the heir apparent to Oda,
Lord Protector of Mikawa.
Did you really think
that girl would make
a worthy match for you?
Uh! Yeah, well, you didn't
have to put it so bluntly!
If you're set on marriage,
I think a daughter of the
Ashikaga would be best.
We're done talking about this!
Sure, stuck between the powerful
provinces of Mino and Mikawa,
Owari's future is bleak,
and the clan's so overrun
with scheming and
backstabbing right now,
there's barely time to think,
but that doesn't
change anything!
Because there's
going to come a day
when you have to
take a stand and fight,
otherwise, who do
you think is going
to defend the Oda clan
against its enemies?
[NOBUNAGA] You know,
you're starting to sound
more and more like
Old Man Hirate.
[jingling]
Takugen Oshou.
It certainly appears
the young master
is making waves in the world.
Could you spare me?
Katsusaburou scolded me the
other day for the same reason.
I was bringing it up more as an
observation than as criticism.
After all, my diverting of
the foreigner's rare goods
through the black market
has proven quite lucrative.
And has greatly improved
the mood of Mino's Saitou clan.
Additionally, children
left dispossessed by the war
have benefitted.
It's a good system all around,
wouldn't you agree?
However, it is a well‐known fact
that human desire has no limits.
Here.
If the equilibrium is
disturbed even slightly,
it will likely
vanish in an instant.
Just like the bubbles that
form inside that teacup.
[NOBUNAGA]
Hey! I'm home!
I wonder where everybody is.
What's going on?
You could've at
least invited me.
Young master!
We would like to know
where you acquired this object!
How did you...?
[GOZEN]
Kanjuurou told us.
He saw you in
possession of this item.
So I ordered
your rooms searched.
That's an import from
the foreign barbarians.
Odd it was found in your
room right after there was
a discrepancy reported
with the ship's inventory.
Where did you obtain it?
I found it by the river.
The river?
Who do you think you're kidding?
I figure the thieves must not
have been able to fence it
and threw it into the water
as they were passing by.
And I suppose everything
in your hidden room
came from the river as well?
[cries]
[HIDESADA]
Young master.
I believe you owe us
an explanation.
Please speak the truth
and I'll take your word.
I, Hirate, swear
it upon my name.
[NOBUHIRO]
Sorry I'm late.
[NOBUNAGA]
Elder brother!
Don't mind me.
I was just wrapping up
some falconing
and decided to pop
in for a minute,
and see what the
excitement was about.
Sounds like they're really
putting you through the wringer.
No surprise there.
So where were we?
We won't tolerate you
protecting your brother.
This matter only
concerns Nagoya.
That's where you're wrong.
Do you expect me to sit silently
by while he's branded a thief
without a single shred of proof?
[HIDESADA]
But there is proof.
Do I need to give my
seniors a history lesson?
This castle used to
belong to the Imagawa
before my father
and I seized it.
It makes perfect sense if there
are one or two concealed rooms
we didn't know about until now.
That was several years before
Kanjuurou was even born.
How could it have gone
unnoticed for so long?
[NOBUHIRO]
Is it any shock?
Given the incompetence
of our senior retainers.
Now that that's settled,
let's eat!
[NOBUHIRO]
I'm famished!
I may keel over.
[ROKUROU] What do you
mean you're quitting?
Word of your activities
has gotten out
and endangered
the operation.
There's no way!
[TSUNEOKI] If you keep this up,
it's certain you'll be caught.
I wish it wasn't so,
but there's no other option.
So what about us?
You can quit anytime,
but how are we supposed to eat?
Settle down.
It's not like this is
Kippoushi's fault.
I understand.
It's too dangerous
for you to continue,
but we divvy our earnings
out to the orphans.
We'll find another
way to support them,
after one last haul.
Go on.
Later tonight.
A foreign ship's coming in.
The dock workers
were talking about it,
so I know it's a sure thing.
But after this, it's over.
Why did you agree to
go along with their plan?
This is the last time.
You expect their kind
to keep their promises?
Friendship means
trusting the other person.
Why're you telling me this?
Because I don't have
that level of trust in anyone
at the castle.
Not even my mother.
Huh?
Who are you?
Kippoushi‐sama,
you have to run!
Watch out!
[ROKUROU]
Where's Kippoushi?
No sign of him yet.
We can't afford to
keep waiting around,
they're going to move all the
goods into the storehouses.
Nobody makes a move.
I know him.
He wouldn't go back
on our agreement.
Could've sworn that
little brat was around here!
Dammit!
It looks like
the coast is clear.
You know who those guys were?
[ROKUROU]
One look at you,
anyone can see you
come from money.
You might as well be wearing
a sign that says, "kidnap me."
[HIRATE]
Kippoushi‐sama!
Sounds like your
escort finally showed up.
[NOBUNAGA]
Thank you.
It's nothing,
so don't worry about it.
You saved me.
Don't expect me
to ever forget that.
By the way, what's your name?
Just call me Rokurou‐saburou.
Kippoushi‐sama!
Wake up, Kippoushi‐sama!
Did I fall asleep in my clothes?
Wait a minute.
Were we captured?
Yes, but, for some reason,
we were taken to an estate.
[NOBUNAGA]
Hey! Somebody!
[TAKUGEN] So you're
finally up, Kippoushi‐sama?
[NOBUNAGA]
Takugen!
You snake!
What were you thinking,
kidnapping us?
I'd advise you to choose
your words more carefully.
Once spoken,
they can't be taken back.
And can potentially wound
the person they're directed at.
Like I care!
Katsusaburou!
Get the horses!
Sir!
[TAKUGEN] If you're trying
to catch the barbarian ship,
it's already departed.
It's gone?
The bells' chimes are
signaling the hour is noon.
What happened to my friends?
Where's Roku and the others?
[TAKUGEN] Apparently, they
were arrested for their crimes
by Tsushima's "Faction
of Fifteen," and transferred
to the custody of Oda to
await their punishment.
I should've known.
Father!
[TAKUGEN]
Let this go!
Perhaps you should take
the time to think about
why you weren't allowed to
make it to Tsushima last night.
[NOBUNAGA]
Father!
Kippoushi!
Wait! You're not
supposed to be here!
Stop!
[NOBUHIDE]
What would make you say that?
He's come all this way,
it would be inconsiderate
of us to turn him back now.
Come, and stand by me.
[TSUNEOKI]
We never should have shown up.
[TSUNEOKI] If it ever got out
the heir to Lord Protector Oda
was behaving like a thief,
the condemnations in the
castle would only get worse.
That must've worried
Nobuhiro‐sama.
enough to have him
confine Kippoushi‐sama
and prevent him
from meeting Roku.
Your timing could not
have been better.
I was just preparing to
exterminate a few rats.
Apparently, these filthy
dung‐heap dwelling vermin
got it in their heads it was a
good idea to steal some items
I'd been storing in Tsushima.
Why're you shaking?
Do you know them?
Why am I even asking.
Not as if I believe it but
someone claimed you kept company
with this trash and helped
them pilfer valuables
on the way to my warehouses.
If it were true and my son
were a common thief
I'd become the laughingstock
of the entire realm.
Let's begin. Bring it here.
You're going to use a musket?
So you're familiar
with this weapon?
What a clever boy you are.
Observe.
First you take aim
at your target like so.
The damn thing
went off too early.
Reload it.
Now you see, Kippoushi?
How it works?
You are my heir.
It's impossible for you to be
associated with rats like these.
Because if you were,
then there would be only
one way to resolve this.
With you having
to commit seppuku.
Seems you don't
know them after all.
[ROKUROU laughs]
What grand lords.
More like idiots,
every last one of you!
Just what're you saying?
Someone tells you
he's running around with us
and you believe it?
As a part of our crew?
You guys are a joke!
[NOBUHIDE]
Is that so?
I swear.
I've never seen his
dumb face before in my life.
Then it looks like you die.
Young Master!
Step out of the way!
The thing about muskets,
when you plug the barrel,
you can't fire it.
If you pull the trigger,
you'll be blown away, Father.
Is that true?
Yes.
Even so, it's not like you'd
come away unscathed either.
That may be true.
But it's better than watching
my companions be murdered.
[gasps]
[ALL 3 gasp]
Huh?
Since you admitted
they're your accomplices
then you must also
assume responsibility.
You're saying you'd
slice open your belly
and take their place?
[sighs]
I really don't understand
why you're being
so dramatic, Father.
They say that when
the ship's sinking,
the rats are the first ones
to abandon the vessel.
But, as you said,
the rats are sticking around.
Isn't that proof enough that
Owari Province is in good shape?
Maybe it's true,
and these three rats
are guilty of nibbling
away at your storehouses,
but if that's the case.
If it got out Lord Protector
Oda sullies himself
with exterminating rats,
wouldn't that make him the
butt of jokes all across Japan?
That would be unacceptable.
[NOBUHIDE laughs]
Well, you've
certainly got me there.
Take this.
Apparently you know more
about these things than I do.
I trust you'll use it well.
And one more thing.
I leave that crew
under your supervision.
Do me a favor, teach them not
to nibble at my warehouses.
Yes, Father!
[TSUNEOKI]
Kippoushi‐sama!
What's the matter?
[NOBUNAGA]
That was terrifying.
[TSUNEOKI]
Huh?
The way my father's face looked.
Did you see it?
I was certain that
he was going to kill me!
Even in the face of death,
you stood your ground.
[NARRATOR]
New Year's, 1546.
Kippoushi‐sama came of age
and changed his name.
From that day forward, he was
known as Oda Saburou Nobunaga.
An auspicious name,
signifying one who'll govern
the realm for a long time.
Nobunaga.
I will be counting on you.
Yes, sir!
[NARRATOR] The following year,
Nobunaga‐sama,
along with his guardian Hirate
Masahide and others,
attacked Oohama.
Where an Imagawa
army was deployed.
He was lauded for
a remarkable first battle.
This took place in the spring
after his fourteenth birthday.