(Narrator)
Blue skies....
Fluffy clouds...
(Narrator)
Summertime is all
about....
(Narrator)
...Swimming!
You are proposing
the beach?
Yeah! That's where we
should all go for our
vacation! I mean, it
is summer, after all.
That is true, but
this is no time to be
fixated on relaxing!
Summer is the perfect
time for us to re-double
our training efforts!
But just what kinda
training is THAT!?
Whatever. I give
up... huh?
Hey! Sakura! Guess
what? Lee doesn't
want to go to the
beach!
I was hoping we
could get everyone
to go together...
Everyone!?
By the way, are you
gonna buy that teeny
swimsuit we saw the
other day?
ARGHGHHH!
Actually, I'm
not sure yet.
You should get
it! It looked
fantastic on you!
That was one
hot swimsuit!
[echo]
Hot swimsuit...
H-hot... swimsuit?
I'll meet you at
the store later!
Okay!
(Lee)
(muffled)
Tenten...
Huh?
Time to go! We
can train at the
beach!
How are you gonna
train with a
snorkel in your
mouth!?
(thinking)
Who cares about
training..? I want to
see Sakura's new swimsuit!
Ahhh! He's overheating!
He's about to blow!
"Summer Means Seashell Style"
Did I mention this
hurts? Expansion Jutsu!
[laughter]
Bushy Brow?
Huh??
How come you're
so down..?
[gritting teeth]
Ahhh! What's the
matter, Bushy Brow!?
Your eyeballs are
about to pop out!
It is strange...
but I have been
feeling a bit dizzy!
Maybe you're car
sick... you might
need some medicine!
No. I do not
want to stop.
I will be fine after
a while... My love will
ride the southern wind
of youth...
...and run gaily
across the sands!
(Tenten)
You're not sick, you
nut case! You're drunk
off your own fantasies!
Ohhhh....
(Lee)
This is all happening
because Sakura bought
a hot swimsuit!
My fantasy soared through the
azure winds of my heart! And
runs smoothly over the ocean
...All the way to the
distant islands where
we can be forever alone
together..!
No, no! Jet pack
swimsuits don't
exist!
It's an awesome idea,
but she's flying away,
not running! You are
completely out of control!
I cannot stop imagining
how incredible her
swimsuit will be!
You know what I am
talking about, right,
my friend...?
I won't say I
do, and I won't
say I don't...
Swimsuits are just
synthetic fibers
covering skin....
Yes, she should be
wearing something
all natural...
Something like THIS!
ARGHHHHH!
Yeah those materials
are all-natural, but
why the heck are you
wearing that outfit!?
I felt shells qualified
a standard summer fare.
There's nothing
standard about that!
Only super models
wear shells, and that
was a long time ago!
Hey, Lee! Isn't
this a coincidence?!
You're on the
buss, too!?
We're like
twins, right!?
Guy Sensei!
Rock Lee!
-Alright!
Those are absolutely
the scariest outfits
I have ever seen..!
[seagull cries]
Idiot..! Idiot..!
So, what do you
think, Lee? How
do I look?
What!? Is
it that bad!?
Is what bad?
Excuse me, Tenten.
Where is Sakura!?
Hi Lee..!
(Lee)
Oh! That is it!
Sakura's hot swimsuit
is...
...underwater!
How can we
see it!?
Grrr...
What happened?
Hello there! I see
we've already begun
out training, have we?
Are you training to be a
busty swimsuit model!?
How many outfits did
you bring with you!?
I overheard
everything, Lee.
Time to go. We can
train at the beach.
And I have to tell
you, as your teacher
I'm thrilled to see
how dedicated you are!
and as your student
I wish you'd wear
a normal swimsuit!
I'm gonna make things
tough on you today, Lee!
You can start with
5000 laps around the
beach on your hands!
Woah... you look
even creepier in
that bathing suit
while upside down!
Ready, Lee?
Follow me.
Yes sir!
You came all the
way to the beach
for this..?
[gasp] He is right!
The training is going
to interfere!
I have to find a
way to check out
Sakura's hot swimsuit!
Lee, keep your
focus! Don't zone out!
The sun will have set
before we complete our
5000 laps at this rate!
Uh... correct.
I want to see Sakura's
swimsuit so badly, but I
cannot let Guy Sensei down!
I guess there is no
other choice. I will have
to finish training as
quickly as possible..!
..so I have time left
to see what she is wearing!
[chuckles]
Wow! This looks
so good!
[grunting]
I cannot wait to
see Sakura's hot
swimsuit!!!
This is a great
pace, Lee!
After we're done
here, we'll jump
right into our next
training regimen!
WHAT!?
Yes! Faster, Lee!
We have to ride the
south wind to success!
[sobbing] Sakura's
hot swimsuit!
Much too slow, Lee!
(Lee)
[panting]
You'll never be able to
fry up 5000 servings of
noodles in one day at
a pace like that!
Sakura's hot swimsuit!
ARGHHH! HOT HOT HOT HOT!
You know, this is
really weird.
Bushy Brow is
obsessed with
checking out
Sakura's swimsuit!
Really. And what's
so great about her
suit, anyway?
Nothing that I can see.
I don't understand why
he's so worked up about it.
(Naruto)
But everybody seems to
have their own taste
for these things.
I do feel bad for
him, you know?
I hear ya. I just wish
there was a way we
could help out somehow.
I think there is!
Are you with me?
Yeah!
Next up is 30,000
sideways jumps.
Sakura's...hot...
swimsuit...
Guy Sensei,
what is that?
Huh?
Naruto, are you sure
this is gonna work?
Definitely! Even a hot-
blooded man like Guy Sensei
can't help but be touched
if he sees two sea
turtles crying as
they give birth!
[crying]
Sea turtles
giving birth!?
There's no way I can
train after seeing
such a moving display
of nature..!
Alright, Lee!
We're done for
today!
Yes! Sakura's
hot swimsuit!
And that my
friend, is it!
Wow! Cool!
You didn't say what
to do if he caught us!
Look, everybody!
Snapping-turtle
soup for dinner
tonight!
Sea turtles! Not
snapping turtles!
Time for Plan B!
Guy Sensei may be a strong
man, but he can't help but
be intimidated by a mother
and baby crab of this size!
[evil laughter]
Retreat! Let's get
out of here, ya know!?
Idiot...! Idiot!
[shouts]
It's now time to
practice our Leaf
Hurricane... Alright?
What in the world
is this new exercise
you've come up with?
[gasp] Not an
exercise! Thought
I was going to drown!
Training is well and
good, but all I really
want to do is see
Sakura's swimsuit!
Lee's patience is
surprising... How
much can he take?
Look! Lee and
Guy! Get out of
the water ..now!
It's a shark!
Oh, come on! Do
you people honestly
think I'm afraid
of a shark!?
I'll just blow it
away with my Leaf
Hurricane maneuver!
You'er bringing it
closer to you!
Whoops! Maybe I
should be spinning
the other way...
(Tenten)
That's no good!
Now you're sucking
yourself in, too!
I guess it's time
for my secret trick!
(Tenten)
What's that-- playing
dead!? That won't help!
I am sorry, Guy Sensei,
but I do not believe
the shark will fall for
your act..!
You need to be
more realistic!
I am a dead person!
(Tenten)
Did you know your
nose is bleeding!?
(Tenten)
That blood is gonna
send the shark into
a frenzy!
ARGH! Go away! Get
out of here! Chase
something else! I
ta
ste like leftovers!
You're a genius, Naruto!
Now Bushy Brow can
finally go check
out Sakura's swimsuit!
Go find someone
else to eat!
Leave this job to
me, Sensei! I will
get rid of it for
you!
-WHAT!?
Leaf Huge
Ocean Current!!!
Is that a
new move?
[screaming]
(Tenten)
Why are Naruto and
Konohamaru there!?
Lee... you really
came through...
Oh stop focusing
on your pupil's
progress..!
Talk to me, Lee!
Are you alright?!
[gasping for air]
I think I managed
to chase off that
shark!
(Sakura)
Huh? Now where
did it go?
Huh!? Sakura's out
here looking for
something...
[gasp] This is
going to be my
big chance to
get close to her!
Hm?
AHHHHHH!!
C-could it be?
If her suit is
over here than
she has a big
problem..!
SAKURA!
Huh?
Ahh!
Sakura! I finally
found the ball!
[gasp]
Lee! Have you seen my
swimsuit anywhere
around here? It came
off during the waterspout!
AHHHHHH!!!
I am naked!
(Sakura)
CHAAAA!
Idiot..! Idiot..!
Now I get
it, guys...
So, you were both
trying to help, right?
I just wish we could
have actually done
something for you.
Sorry, Bushy Brow. The way
things turned out, I guess
you just won't get to see
Sakura's hot swimsuit.
(Sakura)
Oh that suit in the
store was too
wild for me..!
I almost got it,
but in the end, I
decided to go with
a normal one!
After all this, I
don't blame Lee for
being disappointed.
It does not
really matter!
I still got to
see Sakura in
a swimsuit!
MMmmhmmm!
So it didn't
matter either
way!?
(Naruto)
I'm starting to
understand Bushy
Brow!
(Konohamaru)
...The allure of
the mundane!
(Sakura)
What the heck
are you talking
about!?
(Narrator)
But you can't blame
a guy for trying! It
is summer, after all.
(Narrator)
Lee and his friends
are spending the day
at the beach!
(Narrator)
And really, what beach
game could be more fun
than this!?
Watermelon splitting!
Yes... the
ultimate challenge...
...A poetic summer
showdown between
master swordsmen....
...who pace carefully
a single piece of fruit...
...putting all their
pride on a single strike!
(Tenten)
That's so melodramatic!
And since when are you
all considered to be
master swordsmen?
(Lee)
I have put myself through
grueling training in
preparation for this day!
[screaming]
Oh brother! I'm not
even gonna begin to
touch that one!
I'm so psyched
about this, guys!
Well, calm down,
'cause I'm gonna win!
I don't care who wins
as long as I get a
piece of that watermelon!
What a drag, but I
suppose I'll play...
Alright, guys! It is
time to go for it!
[cheering]
(Guy Sensei)
Hold it!
Huh??
"Watermelon Wars"
I want you all to
think about this
for a minute...
For ninjas like yourselves,
a game of watermelon
-splitting is so easy,
it's meaningless!
(Tenten)
What is the meaning
of the melon on your
your head, Guy Sensei?
But if we do not play
the game, we will end
up dissecting the
melon as usual.
Yeah, really.
And where's the
fun in that?
Who said you should
dissect the melon
as usual..?
I just said an
ordinary game
would be boring.
So then, what does
that actually mean?
You still don't get
it, do you, Lee?
What is a watermelon
splitting contest?
Concentration and
judgement.
You have the potential
to hone these skills,
and many more.
I wonder which one
is the sweetest!?
(Tenten)
It looks like nothing
more than an excuse to
pick and eat a good melon!
(Guy)
I found a sweet one!
I hereby declare that
today's contest will be the
first-ever all-out Watermelon
Splitting Survival Race!
Watermelon Splitting
Survival Race..?
I think it sounds
kinda fun!
Me too! I'm
so in!
If you're open-minded,
you can think of it as
the perfect training exercise!
Yes! Suddenly,
I am all jazzed!
Oh yeah, and I forgot
to mention, the winner
is going to get the whole
melon for themselves!
A whole melon to
themselves!? How
extravagant!
What the heck?
It would be better
to share it like
normal people.
If you're not confident,
I won't force you to play.
I was worried this
would be too hard
for the girls...
What does that
mean!? We can
handle anything
the guys can!
We won't stand for
you insulting us,
Sensei! We're in and
we're gonna win!
Great! Consider it settled!
The rules are quite simple:
Everyone starts in a
different spot.
And everyone has to
wear a watermelon
balloon on their head.
If your balloon gets
popped, that's it!
You're out!
The goal is to pop
your enemy's balloon
and survive until the end!
The first person to make
it to the finish line and
split the watermelon wins
it all!
Tenten and I will
be the referees,
and enforce the
rules.
Why me, exactly?
You'll be in charge
of the punch-lines.
Gee, what an
honor...
Very well! Let
the race begin!
[whistle]
You can pack up
and o home now!
I will, after
I win!
Lady Hinata!
You know, Sensei, all the
people you've sent on
this mission are highly
trained ninjas...
...I don't think
this watermelon
survival race will
be that difficult.
Think again,
Tenten.
Huh?
This is no ordinary race
they're running. The beach
is littered with traps
unique to the summer.
So they have no
idea what they're
in for?
Not in the
least. Shing!
Okay... "shing"...
If I went straight
through the water...
...It would be a
shortcut to the
watermelon...
...But I would be
a sitting duck trying
to navigate through
this crowd...
I will have to
move very carefully.
Did you figure
it out?
ARGH!
Nothing is quite
as it seems...
Normal summer beach
happenings become
traps in a Watermelon
Survival Race!
He's right, Lee.
ARGH!
A ninja could easily
hide. Especially in this
big crowd of beach-goers.
The first rule of
survival is to move
very carefully...
(Guy)
As a matter of fact, while
we've been talking, someone
has fallen into a trap...
(Tenten)
Wait, it's not
Lee, is it?
Ooooof!
(Tenten)
Choji looks like he's
in pain! What happened?
I ate too much yakisoba and
fried squid and hot dogs and
snow cones and soft serve and
now my stomach hurts!
(Tenten)
You're supposed to
be in a competition!
And you too!
I'm beggin you--
Please..!
I've got you
now, Choji!
Ahhhh! -Oooof!
That was one of
your summer traps
at the beach?
That's right. If you
overeat, you can fall
into Trap # 1
...And that would
be diarrhea! Shing!
I know you're trying
to be cool, but the
"shing" is really
not working...
Hm? Looks like
we've got some
movement in the
snack hut!
Huh?
What's the matter with
you, young lady!? Take
off that funny hat and
get to work!
What!? Wait a minute,
I don't work here!
I just don't understand
you kids today, you're
such whiners!
Hey! Are you listening
to me!? --Ooof!
That was too easy.
Busy summers at a
fast food stall mean
you're gonna need lots
more help! Shing!
That's not so much a
trap, it's just a
problem for the owner.
(Girl)
Hm? What in the world
is this girl up to?
You must be lonely
hanging out at the
beach all by yourself.
Maybe she's down there
spying on an ex-boyfriend!
What a waste! There are
plenty of other fish in
the sea! [laugh]
[laughter]
Excuse me, Mr. and
Mrs. Smart-Alek!
i'm not doing this
because I enjoy it!
You're open!
You lost focus, and
you have to pay the
price, kid!
A lesson learned, see?
Youth is greener on the
other side of the summer
fence... Shing!
That one wasn't a
haiku, it didn't
even make sense!
It's simply a
warning...
When you see other couples
being lovey-dovey at the
beach, it can make you so
jealous, you'll run straight
into the arms of
the first guy you
happen to see... shing!
For crying out loud!
That watermelon's
gonna be all mine,
folks! --ahhh!
Ooof! Ughh...
I'm sorry about that.
[gasp]
Wow! She's gorgeous!
Arghhh!!! That
was cold, Lee!
Nice job, Neji!
I'm always the
distraction...
Why me every time!?
That was a very smart
move, Lee, teaming up
with Neji...
Creating an alluring summer
girl to get Konohamaru to let
his guard down was a brilliant
piece of counter-strategy.
What do you mean,
"counter-strategy!?" None
of this is even remotely
like real traps or survival!
Oh really? Love is all
about survival my dear,
SHING!
Shing, shing, shing!
Is that all you've
got!? Enough already!
Alright, so who's
coming after me?
At least I have
some protection...
There's got to be
a way to get around
that crowd...
Boy, this ramen's good!
There's no telling where
Naruto and Shikamaru will
attack from. I need an
escape path...
Forgive me Neji, but
in this race, I have
to protect myself first!
No action at
the moment...
But this survival
race has definitely
entered it's final
stages.
It's down to four
guys, and I have
to say, they're
all pretty goo-
Oh no! What's
happening here!?
Lee!
Hey, are you alright?
[groaning]
What happened
to you!?
I... I guess I
got in too deep...
(Lee)
She... was so
beautiful...
She appeared before
me as if she had
stepped out of a
dream...
And when she finally
spoke, she told me
she only wanted
one thing...
An emerald more
beautiful than
the ocean...
(Tenten)
What... the what!?
(Lee)
I found I was unable
to deny her...
I spent all my savings
to buy her an emerald
that sparkled brighter
than the seven seas.
(Tenten)
What in the world are
you talking about!?
(Lee)
But as it turned out, she
preferred to have a yellow
diamond brighter than the sun!
Without a thought, she
left me for another man
who was willing to give
her such a jewel...
Yes, that is my
tale of woe...
When I lost her,
I just lost...
everything!
You idiot! You
fell into the
ocean!?
Were you trying to
drown yourself!?
Hey! He said he fell,
but what if he actually
fell for a girl!?
Everyone! Please let
us through! We have
an emergency!
This lovesick fool
needs medical attention!
And, here I am again!
Why does this
always happen
to me?!
Wow, it worked! The
crowd moved completely
back!
It's a straight shot
to the watermelon!
(Naruto)
I've been waiting
for this..!
Naruto?
No way are we
going to let
you get past us!
Well-played, Bushy
Brow! I should have
figured it out!
But just because
you've made a short-
cut, doesn't mean
you've beaten me! ARGH!
-Huh?
You guys are really
making me work! I
hope it's worth it!
D'oh!
Sorry, Neji! But
I had no choice!
Lee! You back-stabber!
AHHH!
Only one of us is
getting his hands
on that watermelon!
And it is going
to be me!!!
[panting]
[shouting]
That melon's mine!
[shouts]
-WHAT!?
All this time it's
been a fake..!?
[chomp] Mmm!
Those boys are
so trusting!
The bottom line is
it was good training
for them...!
[chomp] When all is
said and done, it
looks like I won the
watermelon!
(Narrator)
"Won" might not be
the right word...
(Narrator)
"Stole" is more accurate.
Next time they'll
be more careful
about listening
to smooth talkers!
[frightened gasp]
AND HE SCORES!
[shouting]
(Narrator)
You should never mess with
people! If you're not careful,
they're gonna teach you a lesson
Sorry... everyone...
(Lee)
Yikes! The next episode
is entitled: "I Want
To Be friends With Gaara"
and, "The Rock Lee
Impersonator Strikes!"
Apparently, someone is
going around impersonating me!
(Neji)
Oh no! What's he doing
while he's dressed up
like you?
(Lee)
Well, he's pestering the other
village ninjas to take up his
ridiculous training methods!
Doing random skits at
inappropriate times and
inappropriate places,
and finally, confessing
his love to Sakura
and getting rejected!
(Neji)
So um, how is he different
from the real you?