In a rather stunning
development, today's
episode features an
appearance by that
organization!
For this mission, we must
all exercise an extreme
level of caution.
This added attention is
due to the fact that
we've been assigned
to locate the
Akatsuki's hideout.
And who would they be?
I've heard that name
being tossed around quite
a bit lately.
They're dangerous.
Every member of that
organization is a
powerful S-ranked
criminal.
If left to their own
devices, they could pose
a huge threat to the Leaf
and all we represent.
You're saying they're
set up somewhere around
here?
I understand. I will hunt
down this evil organization
and give them a beating of
a lifetime!
Imbecile!
Looks like Lee was given
a beating first!
Each member of this
organization is
abnormally powerful. Any
individual attempt to
take them on is out of
the question. We are to
observe and report,
nothing more.
Yes, sir!
You have your orders.
scatter!
Infiltrate Akatsuki's
Hideout!
Apparently, these people
move around a lot... so
no matter how reliable
the intel gathered was, I
doubt that we'll be able
to find very much.
No. We will find them if
we look hard enough.
Byakugan!
That's not looking.
You're just making a
scary face.
I found it!
Huh?!
Over that way!
What way?
Oh, come on. A cave? You
gotta be kidding me. This
is such a cliche.
Huh.
What do you think this
is?
Huh? It looks like a
cloak.
It looks familiar.
Uh oh, Tenten.
Huh?
I have stumbled upon a
closet back here.
Look at all the spares!
Hold on, you don't
think that--
There is no doubt in my
mind. These people are
indeed--
[chatting]
Isn't this cloak
absolutely the cutest?
Sure is. I definitely
want one!
Me, too! Let's
all get one!
Sounds good!
--a group of
exceptionally
close friends!
That's not what I was
leading to at all!
Anyway, I've got a bad
feeling about this. Come
on. Let's get outta
here, okay?
I know. And I'm saying
you're wrong!
Huh?!
AGH! The second I
mentioned it, someone
showed up!
Just a minute, Tenten.
Calm down.
But we've gotta hide!
We're gonna get caught!
Hey, do not
worry.
Just let me handle this!
I'm not kidding. You
really have no idea what
true art is, Sasori, my man.
And you call those little
explosions of your art,
Deidara? Get real.
Absolutely. Hm?
[grunting]
This is ridiculous!
Forget about hiding!
We're standing directly
in their path!
I was just uh--
Hey! I know you!
Huh?
Wait a minute... I've
seen this guy before!
What in the world is he
doing here?
That's the kid that foiled
my attempts to get into the
leaf village.
What's he doing here?
What a nice surprise! To
think that we would meet
again way out here!
Who's he?
[laughing]
Come here a sec.
Huh? Oookay.
My shameful failure at
the hands of this kid and
his friends is a
disgraceful black
eye on my record.
I bribed Tobi so he'd
keep quiet,
but who knows what
everyone would say if
they found out about it.
Just being around him is
throwing me completely
off my game.
I'll throw him out
and everything will
be fine. Hmmph.
What is it then, Mr.
Artist?
[gasping]
That's right. He
thinks I'm an artist
or something. Okay, then!
To be completely honest,
you've found the main
office of the Ninja
Comedy Club I work at.
It's kind of like a
Ninja Laugh--
[bird cawing]
Idiot!
That's a completely
different universe! Wait,
so does that mean he's
a comedian or something?
We sacrifice our lives
for our jokes
And so with an iron-clad
resolve, we spend our
days secretly honing and
mastering our material.
If the others find out
that a regular person
snuck in... well...
Well, what?
Worst case, they
treat you as a spy who's
come to steal our material.
After that, they'd
force you to become
one of our Roadies.
And possibly remain one
for the rest of your
life.
No, please, anything but
that!
He's obviously making
all this up, so he's
definitely hiding
something.
I wonder what. Wait,
who cares? We just wanna
get out of here!
With that in mind, I'd
suggest that you-
I see! I bet you're
that new guy Zetsu's
been out scouting,
aren't you?
What? No, you must
be mistaken.
Come on, he's gotta be.
He's wearing our cloak
and everything.
Seriously? That
doesn't prove anything.
Here's a test: What
does the word "art"
mean to you, newbie?
Give it up, my man. Art
is transient beauty that
lasts for but a mere
moment before vanishing.
In other words, art is an
explosion.
You're wrong.
Art is something that can
endure through the ages
and stand strong against
the test of time.
Eternal beauty is
what real art truly is.
Am I wrong?
His head did a 360!
You are. Art is silky
black hair and
spectacularly majestic
eyebrows stuffed into a
flattering set of
full-body tights.
Yeah, I don't
think so.
Heeargh!
[screaming]
What do we do? These guys
are definitely bad news!
This is no time to be
playing around. We've
got important matters
to discuss.
Art is all a
waste of time.
Hm?
There's no money in it,
so what's the point?
Right, Hidan?
What are you asking me
about it for, Kakuzu?
That's just great!
There's two more of
them!
They just had to show up
now, didn't they?
Who's this guy?
Oh, uh, he's--
He's the new
guy, right?
My man!
Ah. Well, I'm this
organizations treasurer.
Money is the only
thing you can count
on in this world.
I don't think I've
ever seen your face
before in the Bingo Book.
But if you've got a
large bounty on your
head, I warn you:
you'd better not
turn your back on me.
Oh man, this guy has...
ridiculously long armpit
hair!
It's not armpit hair,
you nincompoop!
Does it really matter what
he's got? You've got bigger
problems, here.
You're a riot, newbie.
Niiice ooone.
[gasping]
Hey, why don't you
follow the way of Jashin
like I do?
Faith is more important
than any worldly possessions,
if you ask me.
You are all very
unique...
Honestly, he's the
most unique of us all.
And on top of that,
his wretched rituals
take forever!
Watch your tongue! You
stitched-up blasphemer,
you!
[gasping]
That is how
you pray?!
That's no prayer!
He's stabbing pressure
points!
When you break through
the pain, it turns into
ecstasy...
[drooling]
Oh, god... so good.
This guy is totally
freaking me out!
I will have to try that
method for myself.
Here.
Oh yeah, that
is the spot.
Come on! You just wanted
to make that weird face!
Don't forget what's
at stake, okay? You need
to get out of here before
the wrong person comes.
What a ruckus.
[gasping]
It would seem that
we're running a little
bit late for something,
Kisame.
That may be true,
but remember... it's
unhealthy to be in a
rush, Itachi.
They had to show up
the second I said it.
It looks like another
pair has arrived.
Hey, Lee, I know this
one. I've seen him in the
Bingo Book.
Huh?
Itachi Uchiha. That's
Sasuke's big brother.
The one who abandoned
the village.
He and his partner fought
Guy Sensei. They're
Akatsuki members!
[gasping] Why would that
guy be at a Comedy arts
school?
It's all a lie, you
idiot! He made it up!
I knew something was off.
There's no doubt about
it now! This is the
Akatsuki's hideout!
[nervous trembling]
It is the
whaaaaaat?!
A Desperate Escape Plan!
So-So what you are
telling me is that we are
completely surrounded by
members of the Akatsuki?!
Including you, Mr.
Artist?!
Whoa! Settle down!
What's wrong with you?!
Are you nuts?! Don't be
so obvious! He's gonna-
Hey!
What are you two
whispering about over
there?
Are you the new member?
The jig is up! We're
totally doomed! You look
just like Guy Sensei!
Do not worry! I just got
a brilliant idea.
What the heck?
You're just making a
weird face!
You remind me of a
bizarre beast I once
fought against.
I knew it! You didn't
fool him at all!
You know, there's
something fishy
about him.
[gasping]
What an idiot! Even so, I
can't cover for him too
recklessly.
Very well, then. I will
judge just how capable
you are. Prepare for the
initiation.
[groaning]
[struggling]
Oh, no! I have been
caught in a Sharingan
genjutsu. What now?
Idiot, idiot, idiot,
idiot.
If you wish to join our
organization, then you
should be able to resist
a genjutsu of this level.
Give me a break!
Those crows are
way too loud!
He's trapped in some
sort of illusion. I've
gotta slap him with some
chakra to release it.
Thanks, Tenten. The
illusion has been broken.
You broke my hold on you.
Impressive.
Forget me. What about all
that crow poop?! You are
covered in it!
Ah--
Looks like he survived so
far... Good.
Okay, newbie! Now I--
I see everyone's here.
Our Leader!
Did he say leader?!
Holy crap! You mean the
top dog is here?!
Tell me, Konan.
Where's Zetsu?
He said that he would be
late, Pain.
[grunting]
Who's he?
He's the new guy,
apparently.
A new member, huh?
[panicking]
Konan's too smart. She
won't be fooled.
[grunting]
[flinching]
What?
I welcome you.
What the-?! Sh-she is so
hard to read.
Whatever. It's not like
I consider you a real
member or anything.
Did I really just hear
that?
All that for some
flowers? This is so
awkward.
That was exciting, in
more ways than one.
Hey.
Oh, now what?!
My name is Pain.
I am God.
Huh--
I don't think you
can call yourself God
after a pratfall like
that.
Did you see that, Kakuzu?
Total dirt-eating
face-plant!
[grunting]
Oh, yeah?! Almighty Push!
[screaming]
Now you will know pain.
Their leader's a real
jerk-face.
By the way, Leader, may I
ask why you called all of
us to this meeting?
We're going to be
moving forward in
great earnest.
But before that, we
need to make some
preparations.
The preparations for my
ceremony are already
complete.
Another Almighty Push!
But first, we have
business. Hey, Newbie.
I wish to see your
abilities for myself.
[panicking]
He switched topics again!
I agree. We need a
good understanding of how
to use him in battle.
And now to pick...
his opponent.
Only one way
out of this.
Pick me! Let me fight
him!
Hm? Very well, then.
First we were not able to
sneak out, and now we are
locked in a one-on-one
fight!
We're dead. This
can't possibly get any
worse!
Psst! Hey!
Huh?!
Listen, get ready to make
your escape.
What?!
I'll make a smokescreen
with my bombs to blind
them. When they blow, you
run for it!
Mr. Artist, I--
Let's do this!
Hold on! Not so
fast, you two!
What the-?! Who's
this weirdo?!
And what's with that
ridiculous getup?
Allow me to explain
myself...
They're late. If they
missed the rendezvous,
they must have--
--been so motivated,
they explored further
than we agreed on!
No, it's been too long.
Byakugan. Wait a minute!
What the heck is this?
They're all the same
cloak!
Oh, no! That's not
good!
Those guys
surrounding Lee...
... are all members
of the Akatsuki!
What?! In that case,
we've gotta call for
backup.
We can't! There's no time!
If we don't hurry, they'll
get hurt or something worse!
What's he hiding under
that cloak? No, Tenten!
This is bad. But it's
just the two of us. How
can we--
[chuckling]
Just leave
everything to me.
Uh, why am I hiding
under the cloak again?
As I'm sure you're
aware, the enemy knows
my face. The more I can
change my appearance, the
better chance we have of
tricking them. Clever,
huh?
So I'm just part of
your disguise?!
Let's go!
[grunting]
I feel like I've seen
him somewhere before.
Crap! They're on to us!
That cloak would mean-
You're a new member,
too?
I am, indeed. Let me show
you what I'm capable
of, Leader!
Hoachaaa!
[struggling]
I knew that you would
come, Guy Sensei.
For sure. But we don't
stand a chance against
all of these guys at
once.
We've gotta find a way
to escape.
What is the plan?
Force our way through
with guts!
So what you're saying
is there is no plan!
They already know about
my super moves, so I'll
have to hide them.
Okay then!
Different Kujaku!
Different Chicken!
Saying "different" doesn't
hid them, they're the
exact same moves!
There's something fishy
about him, as well.
Looks like that's his
comrade.
[groaning]
Now's my chance!
Ah!
Hm?
Now you've gone and
done it!
Sorry, my man, it was an
accident!
No, it's fine. We'll
settle once and for all
whose art is superior!
[grunting]
Hey, what happened here?
How'd my chakra threads
get snagged?
You idiot! What's your
problem?
That hurt! What is wrong
with you? Explain
yourself, now!
Are you insane?
[gasping]
Let me return the favor.
Tentacle Punch!
[struggling]
[grunting]
Uh, my bad.
Why you little---
I- I know pain.
Whoa! Stop this, now!
Hey, look! They're
distracted. Let's move!
I do not think this is
gonna turn out well.
Have it your way. Let's
rock 'n' roll!
You're on.
Dear me...
I have to stop these
guys.
It appears as though
everything's ready.
Aahhhhhhhhhh...
Know Pain.
That's a lot of chakra
they're building up
over there!
C-3!
Iron Sand Unleash!
Earth Grudge Fear:
Synchronized Arson!
Amaterasu.
My turn. Water Style:
Shark Bomb!
Sacred Paper Emissary
Jutsu!
Almighty Push!
Oh yeah... that's
the spot.
What is that weirdo doing
over there?!
This is no time for
stupid jokes! Run for it!
[fleeing]
[laughing]
[groaning] I should have
known. Nothing good ever
comes out of an encounter
with him.
But at least the Akatsuki
will continue to be
ignorant.
Wow, what a mess. What
happened here?
This is where the
hideout was, wasn't it?
What in the world?
I'll tell you what
happened. That new guy
you sent to us was
nothing but trouble!
New guy? I have no
idea what you're
talking about.
You photosynthetic
peabrain! It was some
thick-browed juice bag
with a bowl cut!
Thick-browed juice bag?
Bowl cut? Oh, I bet it
was the guy Deidara ran
into! Back when he tried
to infiltrate the Leaf
Village!
[grunting]
Hold on, what
did you say?
Oh, I'm not really at
liberty to say.
Deidara paid me to keep quiet
about it, so I shouldn't--
Tobi! Zip it! Now!
I wasn't sure what was
going to happen there!
Still, we managed to
escape in all of the
confusion.
But with their hideout
destroyed, they don't
have a base of operations.
The Akatsuki will
be on the move again
as soon as the remaining
members return.
I am sorry. If I had just
kept my mind on the
mission, none of this
would have happened.
Don't worry about it. We
tangled with the Akatsuki
and came out alive. Even
in danger, we kept our
heads about us.
If you ask me, I'd say
that's a huge success.
Thank you, Guy Sensei!
Ohhh, Lee!
[crying]
Somehow, some way, Lee
and his pals survived
their encounter with the
Akatsuki. But is this
merely the prologue
to a bigger battle?
Wow... I can't believe
that Artist you knew was
in the Akatsuki.
I will not lose to them
next time.
No matter how peculiar
the people in the
Akatsuki are,
I will fight them
off by being even
more so!
There's no need for all
that. I think you're
fine.
Idiot! Idiot!
On The next episode:
"Christmas is the Last
Chance for Love!" and
"Cleanup is a Chance to
Wash Away the Past"!
Cleaning, huh? Are you
going to make us clean
the toilet again? I'd
prefer not to.
Yeah, no thanks.
Deidara's the one who
embarrassed us, so he
should have to do it.
Come on! Let's go tell
him the good news,
Kakuzu!
Wait!
Huh?
There's no toilet to
clean.
Oh, right. We
need to build a
new hideout first.