Welcome back! We join the
gang in the middle of a
big summer trip they've all
been looking forward to. Some
more than others...
This class trip is
going to be awesomely
awesome!
Agh!
We're not here to tell
everyone how great this
place is! This is a
training excursion!
And it's not just
our class, either!
Oh, so that is why
Konohamaru is here
with us, too!
But still, I will enjoy
this! Getting the day off
to visit the old capital
is a rare treat for us!
I want to see the sights
with all of my friends!
That's funny, 'cause it looks
like the only person you're
imagining being with is Sakura.
Regardless, let us all
go out and have a blast!
Yeah!
"A Field Trip to the
Old Capital!"
You're all free to go
sightseeing for the rest
of the day!
I wanna go and
visit the temples!
I think I'm going to buy
some oil blotting paper
from the makeup store in
Kawara.
Oh! Yeah, I wanna
do that too.
I need some as well.
So I will go with
you, Sakura.
She means papers for
blotting the oil on
your face.
We'll split up into groups
of three, and to see who's
in which one, we'll have
a lottery.
A lottery?! No way!
At least this way, I have
a chance to be in the same
group as Sakura!
But I'm on the same team
as she is! I figured that
I'd be in her group for sure!
I know what you are
thinking, Naruto...
Bushy Brow wants
in her group, too!
I will be in Sakura's
group, and there's nothing
you can do about it!
Bushy Brow!
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
[giggling]
[groaning]
Remember, everyone, you
have to meet back at the
inn in three hours!
Okay!
All right, ladies!
Let's go!
So what do you want to
do first? See the temples
or go shopping?
I don't know, that's
a tough call.
Hold it, you!
Please, Konohamaru, I
am begging you, here!
Trade teams with me!
Forget that!
Trade with me!
Uh, you're both
scaring me, guys!
Enough!
[groaning]
Listen, rules are
rules. I won't allow
switching.
But why do I have to
be stuck with Naruto?
Come on! I should be
asking that about you!
There's something you
two need to remember...
Huh?
I expect you to behave.
Anyone who starts causing
trouble will be forced
to sit in their room...
...on their knees.
Us cause trouble?
Never! Right, Naruto?
Righter than Right,
Bushy Brow!
It seems there is no getting
out of this. We will just
have to visit the same places
as Sakura!
Sounds like a plan.
So, Sakura, tell me!
Where do you think your
group is going to head
first today?
They are gone!
Sakura?!
What's the big idea?
You punks just stepped
on my foot!
I am sorry.
Yeah, I'm sorry, too
That's what you
call an apology?
Where ya from?
What school?
Well, I think
Sakura is cool?
No, not what's cool!
What's school?!
You know what, guys?
I think we'd better
teach these punks a
lesson!
We're gonna have to
whoop these chumps!
I do not want to sit on
my knees for causing trouble!
They started it, and if
we don't finish it, we're
cowards!
I am no coward! But if
we fight them, we will be
just like autumn skies to
a flame.
Get it right! The expression
is, like roundworms to a flame!
No, you are wrong! It is,
fly, fly, fly; flutter,
flutter to a flame!
You're both so wrong I
doubt you've ever been
right! It's like moths
to a flame!
And why are we even
bothering to argue about
their argument anyway?!
Here, eat this!
Huh?!
I don't get it!
Where'd they go?!
Ugh, you know, if I hadn't
used the Substitution Jutsu
back there, you two would've
caused a huge scene!
It is all because Naruto
wanted to fight with
those delinquents!
I had no choice after
you went and stepped
on his foot!
You guys! Listen to me!
Hey! You stepped
on it, too!
I do not have time to
argue with you, Naruto!
I have to go and find out
where Sakura has gone!
Not without me,
you don't!
Why do I always have to
get dragged into their
foolishness?!
Hold up, what're we
doing at a temple, anyway?
Remember what Tenten
and Sakura said?
So what do you want
to do first? See the
temples or go shopping?
I don't know.
That's a tough call.
This was simply
our first option!
N-Naruto?
Huh?
Hinata!
Hey, what's going
on, Hinata?
Oh...well...
um...
Stay calm. Just don't
startle her, and eventually
she'll speak.
I know, you don't
have to tell me.
But I really want to
hurry and get to the
next place that Sakura
and her group might be!
So do I, but
we can't yet!
We're a team.
We move as one.
So, I um...
Five minutes later...
Well, uh...
Ten minutes later...
Uhh...
And twenty minutes later...
Um...
We're lucky to
have such nice
weather!
That's the best
you could do?!
[whining]
Uh...
You two...
How dare you hurt
Hinata's feelings?!
[screaming]
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
It is hopeless.
We have completely
lost Sakura.
And it's your fault,
Bushy Brow!
No, you are wrong!
You are the one who
poured the oil on the
fire!
Wait! Oil!
I think I'm going to
buy some oil blotting
paper from that makeup
store in Kawara!
She said oil
blotting paper!
I don't see her
group anywhere!
Wait, what are you
doing now, Bushy Brow.
Sakura will be thrilled
if I buy these for her!
Good idea! I'll
get her these!
[charging yell]
Huh?
Aw, man! Look at the
size of this line!
We do not have
time to waste!
It's that woman at the
front. She's buying
a ton of stuff!
Then we have no choice.
Listen, lady, just
give it up!
Buying all that makeup
is not going to make
you young again, you know!
Oh, yeah?
Okay, thanks so
much for the tip.
[screaming]
Where are Naruto and
Big Bro Bushy Brows?
I gotta find 'em before
it's too late!
[screaming]
Why did it have to
be Lady Tsunade...
And why'd she
hit me too?!
You just had to
open your big mouth!
You opened
yours first!
This is all
your fault!
No, it is
all yours!
Big Brothers Naruto
and Bushy Brows!
Huh?!
What's up, Konohamaru?
Big trouble is what's up!
A bunch of bad guys are
harassing Sakura and Tenten
and won't leave 'em alone!
I tried to protect them,
but those punks were too
much for me!
What?! Sakura
and Tenten?!
Bushy Brow, I know we've
been fighting all day
long, but...
Say no more!
I declare a truce!
C'mon, doll face,
don't be shy!
We'll go eat some of
the old capital's
famous extra-thick ramen.
It's great! They put
green onions on the
top!
We're not going
anywhere with you!
Right, Sakura?!
Yeah! I hate thick
ramen! I like it
brothy!
That's the issue?!
Listen, you
my be cute...
...but don't you get
sassy, or we'll stop
being so nice, you got
it?
You're coming with
us, even if you
don't wanna!
Hold it!
Huh?!
I know that voice.
It's Lee!
Uh...
Hey! It's those two
guys from before!
Let us do it, Naruto!
Roger!
You got it!
This is so dumb, it's
making me dumber just
looking at it!
[attacking yell]
Forget it, Lee!
You can't copy
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
What is with
these guys?!
Now take this! Shimura-
Style Clone Secret Strike!
Wow!
Huh?!
Naruto, we have been so
foolish fighting amongst
ourselves the way we have!
You're right. We've finally
got some vacation time, and
we're gonna get way more out
of it if we both work together!
Good grief, just
look at them...
That was totally
cool, you guys!
Why do they have to
keep wearing those
outfits?
Why don't we go buy
some souvenirs! Come
on, we'll go together!
Sakura!
And so, Naruto and Lee
made up and went shopping
for make-up with Sakura.
Their plan went off without
a hitch. Well, without
a lot of hitches. Okay,
despite the hitches!
But...
Their sensei soon heard
about all the troubles
that they caused, and the
friends were forced to
sit on their knees
together. And they
lived happily ever
after.
How did I get
dragged into this?
Night fell on the field
trip we're calling a
training excursion.
It's now past curfew...
And when she turned
around she saw...
Man, Konohamaru is taking
forever to get back!
Huh?
Well, I got
the drinks!
That is good
work, Konohamaru!
I guess, but it sure
took you long enough!
Come on, give me
a break, Naruto!
If the instructors
caught me, I'd have to
sit on my knees all night!
My heart was racing!
Okay! Our night of
fun begins right now!
So, cheers!
[screaming]
"Girls' Rooms and
Candy Boxes."
You guys, I'm
so sorry.
Come on! Don't you know
when you run with fizzy
drinks they get all
shaken up?!
Easy, Naruto.
So, what're we
gonna do now?
There's just
one choice!
We go to the girls'
room to hang out!
Huh?!
The girls' room?!
Of course! When you are
on a training excursion
that is actually a field
trip, sneaking off to go
hang out with the girls,
is the climax of the
whole event!
Bushy Brow! This might
be your best idea ever!
Yeah! Count me in!
Do they have snacks?
You bet! Of
course they do!
Yes, a girls' room is
like one big box of
sweet treats.
Do you want to come?
Well, no, not
especially.
Then again, I suppose
one of you oafs might
try something funny
with Lady Hinata.
All right. I guess I'd
better tag a long to
chaperone.
Yeah!
You're up for this,
right, Shikamaru?
What a drag. I'm not
gonna go hang out with
some girls.
Shikamaru...
You're so lame
sometimes!
Well, we cannot
force him to go.
So? What's the
plan, then?
For starters, we don't
even know which room
Tenten and the others
are in right now.
And if the instructors
catch us, we'll be sitting
on our knees 'till sunrise!
That is true...
Okay! I'll go scouting
and find the girls' room!
I owe you! After that
fiasco with the drinks!
Are you sure
you can do it?
Just have faith in me!
Please, Big Brother
Bushy Brows!
All right, then! We
are all counting on you!
Wow, Sakura, they're
awesome! Let me see
again! C'mon, c'mon!
Huh? Uh... Um...
I just... Soft drink?
Uhhh...
Man, Konohamaru is
taking forever!
I hope that nothing
has gone wrong.
Maybe one of the
sensei caught him.
I will go take a look.
Hmm...
Uhh...
Sensei, pawn
to 2-D.
This note...
It's definitely
Konohamaru's writing.
And what does
it say?
Hmm, let's see. It says,
"The girls' are in the
last room at the north
end of the hall."
That must mean that
Konohamaru has succeeded!
But where is he?
Why did he just
leave a note?
Neji, you are up.
Byakugan!
[screaming]
Neji!
Hm?!
I saw something no
one should ever see.
What do you mean?
What was it?
A grisly murder scene?
Or a scary ghost
just wandering by?
Konohamaru was stuck
sitting on his knees.
We were right!
Poor Konohamaru has made
the ultimate sacrifice
in order to leave us
this precious letter!
Konohamaru!
He grew from a boy
to a man while we
weren't looking!
Is it really
worth crying over?
We cannot let his
sacrifice be in vain!
We must make it to the
girls' room to hang out!
Yeah!
I think you just want
to go, and you'll make up
whatever excuse it takes!
What do we do?! We have to
get past the Sensei's room,
but if we just walk by,
we'll get busted!
Yeah, we're up against
Kakashi Sensei and
Bushier Brow Sensei.
Are you serious?! We
just have to charge in
and snatch defeat from
the jaws of victory!
I think you mean to
say, "snatch victory
from the jaws of defeat."
The jaws of
defeat! That's
it!
Here's the plan: we send
someone to get inside their
room, splash drinks on their
clothes, and get them both
good and soaking wet!
The two of them will then
have to head to the big
bathroom to get cleaned up.
And we'll take that
opportunity to run to
the last room on the
north end!
Wow, Neji! What
an excellent plan!
Let's get to it, then!
Huh, that's funny. I
thought you didn't
even want to go, Neji.
Hmph!
[whimpering]
Sensei...
[groaning]
Big Brother
Bushy Brows!
Konohamaru, we have a
plan. We will get both
of them to run off to
the bath and thereby
open a path to victory!
Wow! I'm impressed!
You didn't give up!
What's wrong, Lee?
You look a bit under
the weather.
Sensei, I think I have
a fever. Could you please
give me something cold to
drink?
Something cold
to drink?
Hold on, I'll check.
Hm...
Here, drink up.
Now is my chance! I
just have to pretend
to sneeze and do a
Leaf Whirlwind!
Ah!
Achoo!
Ahh!
What?! I missed!
Noooooo!
You sneezed
all over me!
He messed
it all up!
Choji! It's time
for plan B!
Mm-hm!
Sensei, I'm really
thirsty now!
He's not even acting?!
Huh? Oh, help yourself
to anything on the table.
[chuckling]
Thanks, Sensei!
And now he's really
drinking it?!
Choji, do not
forget the plan!
Oh! I forgot!
Ahhhh!
[screaming]
You guys stink
at this!
E-Excuse me!
Huh?
I started a fire and I
can't seem to put it out!
Can you help me?!
They're never going
to buy that, Naruto!
Fine...
Water style,
Bucket Relay!
[grunting]
This is not
going well...
Now go to bed!
Naruto and Big Brother
Bushy Brows' plan has
completely failed!
Those kids sure
are a handful!
Now I'm thirsty.
Oh, right. Choji
drank everything.
Sensei!
I still got the two
drinks I bought earlier!
Oh, how nice of you!
Thanks a million!
Yes!
You don't shake up
carbonated drinks!
My- my eyes!
Now the two of them
will have to go in
the main bath!
They have a
private shower?!
Hurry up!
Huh. The faucet
won't turn.
Is that...
I think it's
Shikamaru's Shadow
Pull!
Hmph!
You guys sure can
be a real drag!
Shikamaru!
Nice one, buddy!
Forget it, I'm
going to the
big bath!
Wait up!
We did it!
You guys rule!
We got past Guy Sensei
and Kakashi Sensei!
To the girls' room!
Full speed ahead!
Well, we made it.
Yeah!
It is all thanks to
Konohamaru bravely
leaving that letter
for us.
You know, Konohamaru.
I'm proud of you!
Mmm...
Big Bro...
But what letter did you
mean? All I did was get
caught and sit on my
knees all night long.
What?! Then
who wrote it?
[burp]
Huh?
[screaming]
I'll explain...
You see, the letter that
Lee and the others thought
was from Konohamaru was
actually written by Kakashi,
who used his Sharingan to
copy Konohamaru's handwriting.
Actually, Tenten, Sakura,
and the girls were in the
second to the last room on
the north end of the hall,
and Lady Tsunade was
in the last one.
Oh, noooo!
You boys, you got
guts, I'll give
you that!
[screaming]
Hmm...
Lee and the others played
right into Kakashi and Guy's
hands- and fell right onto
their own knees.
And there they sat until
the sun came up. But, uh,
maybe we won't wait around
for that...
Guy, it's preview time!
Oh, yeah! I'll do it
sitting on my knees!
Why are you on
your knees, too?
The kids don't get to
do all the training!
I want in on it, too!
Oh, whatever.
Anyway, the titles for
next time are...
"The No-Ninja Jutsu Lifestyle!"
and "I Want to Share an Umbrella
With Sakura."
Whew! My legs are numb!
You handle the rest,
Kakashi!
I did! Pay attention!
Wait, you're numb already?!