You no good stinkin'
Leaf ninja!
You really believe that
you can stop us?!
Woah! Things this week are
starting off seriously serious!
Can Lee's team handle this?!
Just leave it to me Neji!
Hmph.
Hidden Leaf-Ahh!
[Grunting]
Let me go first, Neji!
What are you doing?
Fight them, not each other!
No! This fight is mine!
[Chuckles] Those boneheads are
fighting themselves!
Now's our chance!
Let's get 'em!
What's this?!
I can't move!
Shikamaru! Choji!
We're here to help out!
Huh!
What is this jutsu?
Shadow Possession Jutsu!
You're up, Choji.
On it, Shikamaru!
Human Boulder!
[Grunting]
[Screams]
[Chuckling]
Now that's what I call teamwork!
You can tell they're best
friends!
Teamwork! Best friends! That is
what youth is all about!
"Teamwork Symbolizes Youth."
This is Barbe-Q's, the
restaurant where Lee
and his pals go to relax.
Please, Shikamaru! I need your
help in training how to be a
best friend so I can improve our
teamwork, too!
Aw, what a drag...
Can you actually train to be
best friends?
The young lady asking that
question, and stuffing her face,
is Shikamaru's teammate, Ino
Yamanaka.
Shikamaru and I have been
sharing snacks since we were
little kids.
That's one reason why
we're so close!
I brought some chips
for us to eat!
Oh! Thank you!
[Munching]
I see...
So sharing food is one of the
ways that someone can become a
best friend!
Also!
One friend must get fat!
What?! Hey, don't you call me
fat! I'm pleasantly plump!
Open up, Neji! Just
say, "Aah!"
Ow, Lee! That's hot!
Knock it off!
Yes! It is a hot-blooded symbol
of our friendship! This is sure
to help our teamwork!
Ahh!
Is it even possible for them to
be like Shikamaru and Choji...?
Just one piece left.
Choji, go on.
[Chuckles] Aw, the last piece.
The flavor of the final bite of
meat is the best of all!
Ah ha! I see.
So offering someone else the
last bite of food is also a part
of being best friends!
[Eager Chuckling]
No!
Here, Neji! Take the last bite
as a symbol of our friendship!
Eat this and you will be a
pleasantly plump fatty like
Choji over here!
You and me, outside, now!
Actually, this is a good chance
to work on our teamwork drills.
Even if it is a total drag...
Yes! I am ready to learn!
Hmph.
I have to be cursed
or something.
We'll have a two-on-two
tag team match.
If Choji and I can escape with
this bell, we'll be the winners.
Lee and Neji, your job will be
to try and take it from us
before time runs out.
Hmph.
Each of you is good in
your own right...
...but without strong teamwork,
you'll never get the bell from
us.
All right! Time to
start the drill!
[Exhales]
What's that stance?
He does that whenever he's
formulating a plan.
He's a super genius with an IQ
that's over two hundred!
Okay. I've thought of two
hundred strategies.
Woah, he thinks fast!
Huh? Is Lee devising
a plan too?
Okay! I have a plan!
We beat them up!
No kidding! Nice plan, genius!
I'll start by setting a trap.
You see if you can buy me some
time, Choji. Okay?
You got it, Shikamaru!
[Laughing] I already know how
you two work together.
And two can play at that game!
What?!
Lee's using Shadow Possession
Jutsu!
Eyebrow Possession Jutsu!
[Grunts]
What the heck is that?!
This is an attack where I use
the power of the Eight Inner
Gates in order...
...to release the limiters on my
eyebrows and make them grow!
Ew, gross!
Nice-except it's not!
My expansion Jutsu will rip
right through this!
Expansion Jutsu!
Ow! It's squeezing my brain!
Woah...Scary eyebrows!
Now, Neji! Use the Human
Boulder!
Do what?!
All right, fine.
Eight Trigrams Palm Rotation,
Human Boulder!
Oh no you don't,
I'll show you!
[Screaming]
[Sighs] There. My paper bomb
trap is all set now.
All I have to do is
lure them in.
I've predicted every move they
can possibly make. This is gonna
be way too easy!
[Screams]
[Screaming]
[Grunts]
Huh. I didn't see that one
coming.
[Grunting] I am finished.
Lee! You okay?!
Neji, sorry but that will not
do. It needs...
...it needs to sound more best
friend-ish!
What? Best friend-ish...?
Hmm. No! Lee! Hang in there!
Don't you dare give up. Don't
you leave me alone buddy! Stay
with me Lee!
Stay with me please!
Neji, I...want to thank
you...for the time that we
shared...
...it made me so happy.
[Whimpering]
But I, before I go
I...[Whimpering]
I need to say something. I have
to apologize to you.
[Whimpering]
No Lee stop! Don't
try to talk!
I must. Neji, I am so
very, very sorry.
But the last time that we went
to Barbe-Q's I ate one more
piece than you did...
That's your confession?!
[Sighs]
[Munching]
Neji...See that huge pile of
beef in front of him...?
When he finishes...the last
bite...
...Then I will be finished as
well...
Don't say that! You cannot give
up without a fight!
And then a miracle happened!
[Satisfied Chuckle]
[Gasp] No way!
That last piece of meat stayed
there the whole day.
And for several days after that!
Honestly, it was getting pretty
gross...
It is still there.
Hold on a second...
Is all of this just some kind of
skit that Neji set up to give
Lee more courage?
What?! It's a leather keychain!
I am just not feeling the
emotion of a bond between two
best friends.
Well it isn't really
your style.
You guys just aren't the type to
be all buddy-buddy.
And Choji and I have been
friends forever.
You can't just imitate us and
expect true feelings.
I told you it wouldn't work Lee!
There's just no point in copying
their moves!
All I wanted to do was to think
of a way to team up with you
more effectively!
That reminds me, in the future,
our plans should be focused
around me!
No, Neji! My plans are superior!
That is because...
[Both]
I am simply stronger
than you are!
[Gasp] They're in synch...
I've had enough of all this
nonsense!
As have I! There is no choice...
We must fight to see who is
number one!
I agree!
What?!
Huh?
[Sighs]
Leaf Rising Wind!
[Screams]
Eight Trigrams Air Palm!
[Grunts]
Not bad at all, Neji!
[Chuckling] Same goes
for you, Lee.
What-what is going on? Both of
them are on the same page all of
a sudden?
Lee and Neji don't have what
you'd call a friendly type of
bond.
Their relationship's different
than Shikamaru and Choji's.
But they do want to earn each
other's respect. And they work
together when things get tough.
That's what it means
to be rivals.
All right, now that's
more like it.
Yeah!
No escape! Eight Trigrams...!
I cannot let Neji outdo me!
Air Palm!
Huh?
Jet Lee!
Ahh!
No way! He turned that
into a team attack!
[Screams]
Aww.
[Grunting]
Well I guess it's a draw.
Idiot. Idiot. Idiot. Idiot.
Fight me, Neji!
That's enough for one day.
This suits them better than
being best friends, anyway!
Hey guys...
Huh?
You put up a really good fight
today. I forgive you for what
happened at Barbe-Q's.
Weird.
If I use the Partial Expansion
Jutsu only on my eyes, then I
can seriously crank up the
cuteness level!
Wow, Choji, that is amazing! You
are huge in every way!
[Grunting] Don't call me that
I'm pleasantly plump!
[Screams]
Neji, I bet I can endure
this longer than you!
This isn't the time
for rivalry!
It is always a good
time for rivalry!
Oh, man this is such a drag.
Yes, it's a drag, but it's still
friendship.
And friendship comes in many
forms! Like the form of a giant
rotating ball.
[Birds Squawking]
Ninjutsu is very important to a
ninja, but so is intelligence.
And right now, our friends are
about to take an IQ test to
measure theirs.
This is where we're taking
the test?!
I am a ninja who cannot use
ninjutsu. So I have mastered
martial arts.
But I have to keep my mind
sharp as well!
Intelligence is the ability to
think, plan, and solve problems.
It's a no-brainer that it's
important to have brains.
Being able to think fast is
important too.
Ha! When it comes to being fast,
I never lose!
[Screaming]
Too bad he's just
thinking in circles.
[Sighing]
[Sighs]
For some reason I feel
really dizzy...
Now that's a low IQ...
"The Culprit Is Among Us."
Hello!
Doesn't it seem strange that
we're taking a test here?
Let's just look for Guy Sensei.
He's the one supervising the
test, after all.
Man, what a drag...
Hmph.
[Scream]
That was Guy Sensei!
Sounds like he's upstairs!
[Grunts]
Was it this room?
Ah! It is locked!
Eight Trigrams Air Palm! Huh!
Oh no! Guy Sensei!
Wake up!
Who could have
done this?
Preeeetty sure it was them.
When I heard about this IQ test
I thought I'd come here
beforehand and set up traps.
But Lee and the others showed up
right after he attacked Guy
Sensei, so there was no time.
Lord Orochimaru. I believe we
should just stay hidden and
observe for the time being.
Mhmm.
It seems he's only
been knocked out.
What's that?
Looks like it's his dying
message. Ugh, what a drag...
Hey, knock it off! Have some
respect! Guy Sensei's been
attacked!
By the way, Tenten, just what
did he mean by "dying message?"
Uh! Well uh...it's pretty much
like well you know!
Oh! I understand! So it is like
one of those things!
I am home!
Huh.
Welcome home, Lee!
Mommy's going to be working late
tonight so I left you a
hamburger in the fridge for
dinner.
Now be a dear and eat it all up
before you go over to your
tutors house!
[Giggling]
It is just like a note your
mother leaves for you on the
kitchen table.
It's nothing like that!
That is not right...?
Well, then!
Is it like this?
Uhh, sure.
These punchlines are becoming
a real drag...
It's just a message left by a
victim to help people identify
the culprit behind the attack.
Yeah, we know that! I
already explained it!
So what is this one
trying to tell us?
It looks to me like a
coiled up snake.
Of course! I know who the
culprit is!
[Gasp] He does?
Spirals are Naruto's symbol!
He must be the one
who did this!
[Gasps]
[Heavy Breathing]
Give it up, Naruto!
Just stay back!
[Nervous Breathing]
It is a sad case...but
also a scary one.
Naruto, afraid of flunking the
IQ test, attacked Guy Sensei
so that he would not have to
take it!
Come on! That didn't happen!
She's right, there
wouldn't be any point.
Naruto's team is with Kakashi
Sensei taking their own test.
Guy Sensei wasn't
involved at all.
I see...Very well then.
Oh! How careless!
How could I have overlooked the
clue when it was right under my
nose this whole time?!
Then the culprit must be Choji!
[Gasps]
[Grunt]
The swirl that Guy Sensei drew
is just like the ones that are
on both of Choji's cheeks!
His motive...?
A grudge from not getting to eat
the last piece of beef at
Barbe-Q's!
You were the one who stole that
last succulent bite from me, not
Guy Sensei!
Ahh!
Sorry Lee, wrong again. There's
no way it could have been Choji.
The room was locked, and the
only way in or out was the vent
by the ceiling.
I see...You are right. A fatso
like Choji could not have fit
through.
Hey don't call me that I'm
pleasantly plump!
Never mind Choji! None of us
could have fit through that
opening.
Yes. To get through there you'd
have to have a narrow,
flexible body like a snake.
A snake?
This time he must
know it's me.
This is quite a conundrum.
Yeah, it's like a
crime novel.
Wait, I have it!
I do not think there
was an actual attack!
Solving this mystery must be the
IQ test we are here for!
Lord Orochimaru, what should we
do? You heard what they all
said.
[Chuckling] I have a plan, we
can make this work for us.
[Grunts]
You are correct Lee,
brilliant deduction.
Guy Sensei, your voice sounds a
little funny. And you are
talking strangely.
I just caught a little cold.
[Fake Coughing]
Okay...But then who's the Guy
Sensei that's knocked out here?
[Stuttering] No, well that's
because he's my twin brother. I
asked him to come help me and...
Oh, wow! You have a twin
brother, Guy Sensei?!
Indeed. He works at a bar now
but dreams of becoming an actor.
My younger twin, Golden Guy.
Great. Yet another
drag to deal with.
Listen, if this isn't an actual
IQ test, then I'm out of here.
Wow, Shikamaru, you've been
complaining this whole time.
Get serious, would you?!
Huh!
Anyone who's unsure of
themselves is free to quit.
It's time to begin my survival
IQ test, and it's terrifying.
For if you fail you will wake up
in hell.
Sounds exciting! I accept
the challenge!
The first question...
Hmm.
Hmmm.
Hmm!
I can't think of any questions.
It's hopeless. Lord Orochimaru's
IQ is too low.
Wait I know! Try to say
"pizza" ten times fast!
I think my IQ is dropping just
watching this!
This is the test I was
born to take!
Here it goes! Pizza, pizza,
pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza,
pizza, pizza, pizza.
Now what is this?
Feetsa!
[Gasps]
Ahh!
What an impossible
question to answer!
It's a good thing Lee's IQ is
about the same I guess.
And the next question is...What
in the entire world is a dog's
favorite food?
What are you talking about? This
isn't an IQ test, it's just a
bunch of riddles!
I know, Pup-sicles!
Ahh!
Belgian woofles?!
The right answer's a hot dog
what else would it be?!
Ahh! Of course!
[Laughing] But the next one is
even harder...
Ahh!
What could it be?
The Big Balloon Burst Game!
Lord Orochimaru, you've become a
lowly variety show host!
With every incorrect answer, the
balloon will grow bigger!
You won't be able to stand the
tension waiting for them to pop!
And worse...the fate that waits
the person whose balloon bursts
first...
...is a boiling hot bath and
scalding hotpot!
Ah! This is one
intense IQ test!
No! This isn't an IQ test at
all! Something is seriously
wrong here!
Ah! Just stop!
It's a drag, but I guess I
gotta save them...
Huh? What is this?
What's going on?!
My body's moving on its own!
Oh, no! Stop this!
No! Don't do this!
[Struggling]
[Screaming]
No! Don't you dare
push me in! Ahh!
[Screaming]
No more! I give up!
It was you?!
Of course!
How dare you try to deceive us!
Ahh!
I suppose the jig is up. But you
don't really believe that
you'll leave this building alive
do you?
[Grunting]
[Chuckling]
Shikamaru's genius IQ of two
hundred is firing on all
cylinders!
In an instant, he's calculated
two hundred setups and
punchlines ahead!
Lee sets it up by mishearing
"building" as "pudding." The
enemy counters with a fancy
chestnut pudding...
Neji reappears and looks inside
them with his Byakugan.
And Lee uses the Sexy Jutsu,
cause things weren't ridiculous
enough already!
Guy Sensei comes to and attacks
with a Shimura Style Secret
Strike.
Choji does something in the
background, but it's not
funny, so no one sees.
Then Tenten says the punchline:
"Guy Sensei, behind you!"
So now, we wait for
that to happen.
What kind of prediction is
that?! And how can you just sit
and wait in a situation like
this?!
Huh?
[Heavy Breathing]
Ahh! They showed up?!
We will fight with sushi! That
is how we roll!
Come on you don't have
to be so shellfish!
[Screaming]
Mind blown.
[Chuckles] So, Shikamaru
heroically fought off
Orochimaru.
Again proving brains are
stronger than brawn!
[Laughing]
Hey, don't predict my narration
too! I need this job!
Next week..."A Field Trip to the
Old Capitol!" and "Girls' Rooms
and Candy Boxes!"
Judging by the
titles, I predict-
Hey! Shikamaru, don't
spoil the next episode!
You sure? I was gonna drop a
hint that would solve every
problem.
It is more fun anticipating
the unknown!
Yeah! Well said Lee!
I will enjoy waiting to see what
color Sakura's pajamas will be!
I take it back...