As always, Rock Lee spends
his days working hard to
become an outstanding ninja,
even if he can not use ninjutsu.
However, he's also
working hard to find
romance!
This is Sakura Haruno.
She's a member of Naruto's
team, but what's more, she's
the target of our dear Lee's
amorous affections!
What pretty flowers!
Hi, Sakura!
How would you like to
go on a date with me?!
Ahh...Egh...
[gasp]
I'm sorry. It's
just that I...
...don't like thick
eyebrows.
Ahhhhh!
"Love Is a Part of
the Springtime of
Youth!"
Why, oh why?!
Yet again, Sakura has
turned me down and
broken my heart!
Get a grip, Lee! She just
said no to a date. You
don't have to act so beaten
up about it.
I am not beaten up! It is
just that with her, my heart
is vulnerable, and she has
landed a critical hit...
Too bad that it
wasn't actually
fatal...
If you ask me, this just
proves guys don't have
anything even close to a
clue about how women think.
Who in their right mind
would fall for someone
who just jumped in front of
them and blew them a kiss?
Oh?! Then how can
I win her heart?!
Don't try so hard.
Let's see now, maybe
you could play it cool?
Play it cool?
Of course!
You sure do have a messed
up idea of what cool is...
So how should I act?
Well, that's not so
easy to explain.
Very well, then. I will
set up a situation to
learn a women's feelings.
[cheering]
Why did I agree
to this?
This day is all about
me! Uh, I mean the truth!
I must learn what
women like about men!
What do you like, Nejimi?
Well, they say girls like
tall, dark, and handsome
men...
Thanks so much! That
is very helpful pretty
lady. And just who is
you type, Tenko?
Well, I don't think it's
enough for a boy just to
look good.
Wait, what do you mean?
He's gotta be naturally
kind, too! And always
give me lots of presents
to keep me happy!
Oh, and be open and honest
about his feelings. But
still take charge every
now and again.
A guy like that would be
the absolute perfect man
for me!
Okay! It was worth
casting that genjutsu!
What're talking about?
That was just a skit!
Be naturally kind, keep
her happy with presents,
remain open and honest
with my feelings, and
take charge every now
and again. That is what
a really cool guy does?
Uh... I guess so.
Pretty much...
Understood! With your
teachings I will become
the coolest guy ever!
Now I will launch another
romantic attack on Sakura!
Hope he'll be okay...
Hey!
Huh?
What's wrong?
I'm supposed to warn
everyone about the rogue
ninja that are hiding on the
outskirts of the village!
[gasps]
Hey, wait. Where's
Bushy Brow running
off to?
A journey of love...
What's that mean?
Hey, Naruto, what do you
think it is that makes a
guy cool?
Ha! That's easy! Treating
people to ramen of course!
Serves me right
for asking.
Well, I don't really know,
but people who protect those
who are important to them,
I guess.
Idiot...Idiot...
[sigh]
Maybe I'll take a
little break.
Hello, Sakura!
Lee?!
The first part of being
a cool guy is natural
kindness!
One moment! Let me
clean that filthy
bench!
If i did this harder
it would be great arm
training!
Ahhh!
Wow, you really
love cleaning.
All set!
Uhh...
Hey, Lee!
Tenten?
Lee, listen to this-
I understand! You are
here to see me acting
cool, right?
Good timing! I am applying
your lessons on how to be
cool right now, and everything
is going great!
No, just listen to me!
There are some rogue-
But I am just getting
started! Now check this
out!
Wait! Ugh...
Huh?
The second part of
being a cool guy is
keeping her happy with
presents!
Here, Sakura! For you!
Uh...
What?!
Ah! Bees! I like the
flowers, but I could
do without the bees!
Do not worry!
I will pummel them with
precision punches!
Ah! Yah! Yi! Yah!
Yi! Yi! Yah!
The only one he's
pummeling is Sakura!
What's wrong with
you, Lee?!
Ahh! I am sorry! I was
not trying to hit you,
Sakura! I swear!
What a disaster!
I must move on!
No! The third part of
being a cool guy: be
open and honest about
your feelings!
Uh...Sakura. I wanted
to talk to you!
This is uh, hard to
put into words, but...
Lee?
Uh...
Ahhh! You ugly beast!
Ugly...
Uh...
That's what you
wanted to tell
me?!
Ahhhh!
[groaning]
It is getting worse!
My only chance now is
the fourth part of being
a cool guy!
But still take charge
every now and again...
I will take charge, plant
a kiss on her, and steal
her heart!
Don't try this
at home, kids.
Sakura...
Ahhhh!
Chaaa!
Lee, you're a jerk!
Just stay away from
me!
Uh...
Boy, what could have
gotten into Lee?
But then again, maybe
I was a little too
harsh on him...
[gasp]
Uh, you don't have to be
so upset, Lee. Sure, it
didn't go well, but don't
be such a sad sack!
Sad sack...
Sakura...
Look, just take
another whack at
it!
Whack...
Sakura...
Come on! Cheer up, would
ya?! The Lee I know would
bounce back!
Back...
Sack...
Sakura...
It's no use, he's just
getting more depressed!
Plus, he kinda forced
that last one!
Ahhhh!
There you are!
Neji!
Did you forget? You
know what Naruto said.
I'm supposed to warn
everyone about the rogue
ninja that are hiding on
the outskirts of the village!
Huh?
Oh, yeah! That's
right! I forgot!
They were spotted
somewhere in that
area over there.
That way...
Is where...
Sakura! They are in
for a surprise!
Keep your shirt on!
Ahhhhh!
No, Lee! Come
back here!
Back luck for you. We
can't let you live now
that you've seen us.
[chuckling]
What do I do?!
I'm outnumbered!
Hm!
Now die!
[gasp]
Agh!
[groaning]
Hornet Stinger!
Huh? It's Lee!
Uhh... Give me
a second...
You made yourself dizzy!
Who's this guy?! And
where'd he even come
from!
Who cares? Get him!
Lee! No!
It is okay! Sit
tight and watch!
Hah! Ahhhh!
[fighting grunts]
Does he really
need to spin?
[groaning]
And that takes
care of that!
But Lee...
Why did...
After I said those
mean things to you...
But none of that
matters.
Huh?
I do not need a reason
to protect the people
dear to me!
[stunned gasp]
Let us go home, Sakura.
Uhh-ahh!
Uh...
Oh no you didn't!
Chaaaa!
Ahhhh!
Idiot...Idiot...Idiot...
[humming]
Tenten!
Huh?
Ahhhh!
So I guess you
blew it, huh?
Yes...
It seems that I am
just not cool.
That's not true! Come
on! You're plenty cool,
Lee!
[surprised gasp]
After all, you protected
your friend!
[crying]
Uhh...
How sweet, Tenten!
Ahhh!
Ahhhh-hah!
Ahhhhhh!
Oops! Sorry!
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
The journey of love isn't
finished in a day. Remember,
everyone, sometimes it's best
to play it cool!
A great poet once wrote,
"Love makes both people
involved do crazy things."
Now the question is: will
the same thing happen to
Rock Lee and the girl he
has a crush on?
[sigh]
Whatever can I do to
convince Sakura to fall
for me?
Well, you can start by
not being so forward.
What I think you really
need to do is try a
more subtle angle.
Huh?
An ankle?
No, I said, "angle!"
You gotta be more casual!
Just send her a letter or
something. Maybe a love
letter!
A love letter!
"Love Makes Both
Sides Crazy."
This is perfect! She
will find my letter,
and then...
What's this?
Dear Sakura, to me, you
are like the pickles that
come on the side with curry
and rice. Even just thinking
about getting a plate of
curry that does not have the
pickles, reminds me of the
time at summer camp when I
got homesick because they
did not make curry like my
mom does. Merely the thought
of that moment is enough to
move me to tears.
What the hell
does that mean?
It's poetry, sheer
beautiful poetry!
Who could've written me
this wonderful romantic
letter?
Oh! And sent this
beautiful present!
That would be me!
[gasp]
Oh, Lee! No one has ever
said something so beautiful
to me!
Oh, Lee...
Yes, Sakura...
Oh, Lee!
Yes, Sakura!
I am yours.
Uh... What is up
with your face?
[humming]
It is all going
according to plan,
so far!
Now I just wait
till she reads it!
Ahhh!
W-What?!
That is not the letter
I wrote to her!
W-What is going on?!
Someone else sent
one, too?!
And just look how happy
she is! That can only
mean one thing, that she
is very excited about
receiving a love letter
from someone else!
Farewell, my youth! Hello,
crushing weight of my age!
It is only the second episode
and I have already lost the
heroine forever!
What's wrong, Bushy Brow?
You look really depressed.
[groaning]
Is that?!
It is! She has a
love letter from
someone else!
Someone else sent one?!
All right, who was it?!
I do not know,
but Sakura...
She is so happy to
have gotten it!
[giggle]
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
I forgot. You like
Sakura, too. Right,
Naruto?
Yeah, we're like two
peas in a pod, huh?
No, we are not!
Sakura is mine!
Wanna bet?!
She's gonna
pick me!
[growling]
Look, Bushy Brow,
fighting each other
isn't going to help
anything.
So what are we
supposed to do?
I think I've got an idea!
[humming]
Okay, all we have to do
is steal the letter before
Sakura reads it.
Of course! Because that way
she will never know what it
said, and the truth will be
"lost for words."
No, I think you mean,
"lost in translation."
No, "lost to the ages!"
Then I will blast Sakura's
bag right off her shoulder!
Wind Style!
Huh?!
I didn't think he could
use ninjutsu! When did
he learn that?!
Leaf Revolution!
That attack blows!
That's nowhere near
enough wind. Just leave
this to me!
Uh, Naruto,
what is that?
Listen, if you're gonna
snatch someone's purse,
you don't want a sad little
gust of wind, you need-
Please don't try
this at home, kids!
...Heat of the sun!
At least I think I
remember reading that
somewhere!
Boy! It's getting hot!
Ahh!
She is going to put her
handbag down! Nice, Naruto!
[gasp]
Uh-oh...
That was pointless. With
your hands full, you
could not grab her bag.
Just hang on! I still
have my secret backup
plan!
[grunt]
[groaning]
My alarm did not go off!
I will be late for my
first day of school!
That's it, Bushy
Brow! Keep it up!
[gasp]
[groaning]
Watch where you're
going, would ya?
[bell ringing]
[gasp]
Huh!
It's you!
It is you!
I call this my, "Crash into
her while eating toast on
the way to the first day of
school, see her in homeroom,
and point and shout,
"it's you!", backup
plan!
[groaning]
[stomach growling]
Ahh!
Ah...
[groaning]
Ah! I am so sorry!
Are you hurt, ma'am!
Hold on tight! I will
get you to the hospital!
Bushy Brow! You're
killing me here!
[sigh]
This is getting
us nowhere.
And we're getting there
fast! Alls we've done is
put her on guard even
more! At this rate,
she won't want to open
her handbag ever again!
Open her handbag...
That is it, Naruto!
Huh?
We will have
her open it!
What?
Hey, Haruno!
Huh?
Stop! We must
inspect your bag!
What?! Hold on!
Who are you guys?
Guidance counselors sent
to put a stop to any
behavior that is unbecoming
of a ninja from our village.
No, I mean...
Guidance ninja!
What the heck's
a guidance ninja?
We just need to take a
look in your bag. We've
had problems with a whole
lot of ninja lately.
Carrying items unrelated
to their mission, ya know.
Uh! What items?!
I'll just have to...
Wing it!
Sorry for the
trouble! Now...
Hey, hold on!
No! It is not
here, Naruto!
C'mon! What're you
doing, Bushy Brow!
Hurry it up!
I am trying to
tell you-
Are you finished?
Uh... Just a
moment longer!
Uh... Faster!
Wait! Almost done!
[gasps]
[shocked breathing]
Are those really
Sakura's panties?!
No! No, this is
not the time!
I have to concentrate
on finding that love
letter!
But then again, this
may be the only chance
that I ever get to see
them in all their glory!
No! What is wrong with
me?! Naruto would be
disgusted if he knew!
Even with those panties
staring him in the face,
Naruto is focused on that
love letter!
Wait! He is completely
focused on the panties!
Naruto!
Oh! Right!
Can you guys please
hurry this up?
Uh, just a sec!
Almost done!
It looks like you are in
need of some guidance!
You are hiding something
from us, Haruno!
[shocked gasp]
Like what?!
Your reaction
just proves it!
If you have black panties
in there, then you probably
have a black bra, too!
A chunin is too
young for-
Agghh...
What in the hell did
you just say to me?!
[screaming]
Oh no! I sent
'em flying!
Huh?
Wait, it's a girdle?!
That is so misleading!
Why does she have that?!
Come to think of it,
she said her stomach
was bothering her.
Never mind that! The plan
was a bust, but now we
have her handbag!
All right...
The only thing left to
do is grab the love
letter the other guy wrote!
Y'know!
Ahhhh!
Huh?
Naruto fish cake?
Pickles?
Wait! That's my letter!
Huh?
What are you
guys up to?
Oh! We, uh...
Did you see any
letters land over
here?
I got two love letters
out of the blue today.
I don't know who
sent them, though...
What?!
That's such a shame.
I really wanted to
read them later, too.
I see. So the other
person was you, Naruto!
Bushy Brow, you...
Ahhh!
Don't worry! I'll explain.
You see, both of them snuck
a love letter into Sakura's
handbag!
Aw, man!
[groaning]
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
So they had no idea and
ended up destroying both
letters, huh? That's not
surprising!
Do you think this
mess has damaged
their friendship
at all?
No. Apparently
just the opposite.
How so?
Right now, they're both
hard at work on a combined
love letter.
We need to put much
more emphasis on curried
vegetables in this section!
No, I'm telling you, a
sentence about ramen
is perfect!
"Love makes both people
involved do crazy things."
That was certainly true
today for Lee and Naruto!
I'm calling a
post-mortem!
Why are you so
mad, Tenten?
I told you the last time
that I wanted a serious
fight, but...
Next time on Rock Lee and
Friends, "A Competition
with the Genius Ninja, Neji,"
and "Tenten's Must-Win Battle!"
[gasp]
So that's-!
There you go, Tenten!
The serious fight you
were looking for!
I'll do my best!
We both will!
Yeah!
By the way, I've
already given up.