Normally our friend Rock Lee
is focused on seeking a path
to greater strength. But
today, he's kicking back and
in high spirits!
[humming]
I am so happy right
now that I could just
dance!
The reason Lee's excited is
because his beloved sensei,
Might Guy, the man he
emulates in every way, shape,
and haircut, is returning
from a mission.
Please hurry! We
cannot be late!
Actually, we can. We
really don't need to
welcome him back.
Today we will obtain
greater strength!
Guy Sensei promised!
[roaring]
Monkey Style! Snake
Style! Preying Mantis
Style! And Badger Style!
Ahhh!
That last one looked weird,
though. How does making a
circle like that resemble
a badger?
Excellent question, Tenten!
It represents the badger's
instinct to burrow when it
sees an opening.
You mean, it's so
embarrassing that you
just want to crawl into
a hole and disappear?
Well, I suppose. That's
the general idea, at least.
Lee, you understand,
right?
No, sir! Not
at all!
Really? Maybe this
technique's too
advanced for you
three.
Guy Sensei, I would
rather you teach us
fighting styles that
can be put to more
practical use.
Your kempo skills are
incredible to watch, but
they are too difficult
to get the hang of!
I feel like there must
be a style that is more
suited to the skills
that we possess.
Hmm...
Very well, then. Maybe
if I create a brand new
style, you'll understand
what I was trying to say.
You will create an
original kempo style
designed just for us?!
Yup! Leave it to me!
Uh, are you sure,
Sensei? It can't be
that easy to create
a whole new style!
A man never goes
back on his word.
Besides, it's just a whole
new fighting style! Coming
up with a few of them will
be an absolute breeze!
Do you have to shake
like that when you
say it?
Idiot! idiot!
I promise you.
I will teach you all a
brand-new kempo style
when I return from my
next mission!
Hnnh!
I cannot wait to learn
that new kempo style!
[crowd chattering]
Huh?!
What do you think
is going on here?
They're bringing in
someone who got arrested
for lewd acts.
What, seriously?
Lewd acts? Ugh,
how gross!
I wonder who it is!
Some disgusting sicko,
I am sure of it!
Look! There he is!
[shocked gasp]
[screaming]
Guy Sensei, why?!
"Guy Sensei Didn't Do It!"
The victims in this
incident all told us
the same story.
Welcome, welcome, come
in, come in! Welcome to
Shimura Hot Springs!
[screaming]
Basically, Guy kicked
down the wall separating
the men's and women's
baths while wearing that
ridiculous outfit. And
then he charged into the
women's bathing area.
That guy's one
heck of a pervert.
Really, Guy Sensei?
This isn't the time
for sparkly teeth.
It's hard to believe
Sensei would do that.
It's not his style.
That is right! Guy
Sensei is well known
as the Noble Blue Beast
of the Leaf!
Yeah, the guests at the
hot springs sure thought
he was a beast, all right.
That is not what I
meant! Yes, Sensei
can be a bit different-
I wouldn't say
different, more
like deviant.
You are wrong!
Give it up, Lee.
She's got you beat.
Hm. One thing's uncertain,
though. We don't know why
he did it.
Sensei, please tell
us what happened.
You're going to be
branded a pervert!
Sensei!
Please, you have to clear
up this misunderstanding!
And then teach us that
new kempo-
Lee, you fool!
Where did that
come from?!
A thought came to me
while they were putting
me under arrest. My ninja
way is to make you just as
strong as I can.
But simply handing you
answers is not the way
to make you truly strong.
Guy Sensei...
So to that end, I have
a mission for you three.
What do you think I
was really trying to
do on that day?
You must uncover the
truth on your own!
But, Sensei...
I'll gladly give up my
future as a ninja if it
helps my beloved pupils
to grow even stronger!
Oh, boy. He's staking
his whole reputation
on us.
Idiot...Idiot...
That's the town where
the Shimura Hot Springs
are.
Guy Sensei can be
such a pain!
He could get out of that
jail any time he wants,
but he's staying locked up.
Staying locked up...
Perhaps he was trying
to drive home his lesson.
Remember? When he talked
about Badger Style and
the instinct to burrow
into an opening?
Yeah, I don't think
it's anything like
that...
But...
I think we should
split up and retrace
Guy Sensei's steps.
Maybe we can
find a clue.
It is hopeless!
All that, and I have
no idea what-
No, of course you
don't! You didn't
even try to get any
intel at all!
I most certainly
did try!
Guy Sensei has staked
his entire future as
a ninja on me, and I
intend to give it my
all in searching
for the answer!
Idiot...Idiot...
Where are you
going, Lee?
Where else?
To the hot springs!
The jets and drains
are holes! Just like
his Badger Style lesson!
Oh, drop it already!
If we don't find some
real answers soon, then
Guy Sensei is gonna be
branded a pervert for life!
You keep running to
these random places
with no good reason!
Do you even want
to save Guy Sensei?!
Uh...But, Tenten.
[clearing throat]
You're right that Lee
is at fault for not
helping us more.
But at the same
time, I think he
has a point, too.
The hot spring's the
scene of the crime,
so we should check
it out.
[sigh]
All right...
I suppose that I have
been running around a
bit randomly. Tenten
was correct to get
upset with me.
But when I see an
opening, I want
to dive in!
[gasp]
Hold on, is this...
Ooh, mysterious!
What did Lee see?!
Time passed, but the three
did not return, and finally
the day of Guy Sensei's
release arrived.
Listen, are you absolutely
certain about this, Guy?
Of course! I'm sure
that my pupils will
clear my name.
It's been a long
time, Might Guy.
Who are you?
A while back, this guy
ran us through the wringer,
and we haven't forgotten!
At long last, we've
come here to get
our revenge!
That's right!
Get him!
Not on my watch!
Huh?!
Lee!
Where have you been?!
I have followed my
instincts and burrowed!
Huh?
Yes, I see...
I understand what
you meant, Sensei!
We cannot ignore even
the tiniest of openings!
We must always dig and
probe!
That is how we unearth
our inner power!
That is the wisdom
you wanted to impart
to us!
Wait...
These are...
After seeing that mural,
you dug and you probed
in order to create a new,
original kempo style...
..."White Swan" Style!
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Just get out of
the way, kid!
[growling]
[gasp]
Why, you!
Hidden Leaf...
Un...
Deux...
Trois!
Huh?
Not to shabby.
That's just the beginning!
Wait 'till you see what
this training has really
taught us!
You little...
Neji!
Why me?
Hidden Leaf...
...Pas de Deux!
[screaming]
Nice one!
Uhh...
Yeah, us!
Not bad, but it
could be better.
Agh! That does it!
You're going down!
[gasp]
That's...
... A paper bomb!
He's going to blow up
Guy Sensei with it!
Now die!
I'll-
No, just let me
handle this!
[growling]
[sigh]
I wish I hadn't promised
them a new style so hastily.
Now what do I do?
Takakura? Matsudaira?
No, not those...
Whoa! Of course!
Hm!
Ahhhh!
Bring it on! Block
one! Block one!
Block one!
No way! Are you
kidding me?!
Shimura Style
Secret Strike!
[screaming]
Wait, that worked?!
Is this it, Sensei?
The new kempo style?
I was so excited by the
idea, I couldn't resist
trying it out right
then and there!
Of course, I may have
overdone it just a
little bit.
Oh! When you settled down,
you realized you'd kicked
a hole in the divider
between the rooms!
Shimura and the Shimura
swans inspired me, so I
named it "Shimura Style"
after Shimura!
Okay! We get it!
What's wrong, Lee?
I have such a
long way to go!
In the end, I was not
able to come up with
as good a solution as
Guy Sensei came up with!
That's not true.
Ah?
Don't beat yourself
up, Lee! Even if your
idea wasn't the same,
it still came the
closest to Guy Sensei's,
and it's certainly just
as weird!
You guys...
Besides, you created
an excellent kempo
style, too!
With even the most
innocuous of objects, and
with the most enchanting
of costumes, you just do
enough hard work...
...you will become
stronger!
Yes, sir!
Now come with me, Lee!
We'll merge and refine
our two styles and create
an unrivaled new kempo
style that only the
two of us know!
Double Shimura
style form Shimura!
Just stop it!
Idiot...Idiot...
Un, Deux, Trois!
Well...
At least we managed
to keep Guy Sensei's
reputation intact.
He may not be a deviant,
but he's definitely
decidedly different.
You know, Neji. That
outfit actually looks
really good on you.
I want to crawl
into a hole!
Ever determined to become
as strong a ninja as Guy
Sensei, Rock Lee runs full
speed down the path of youth!
But what if there were
someone who completely
outclassed his beloved
sensei?
Were about to find
out! Why else did you
think I brought it up?
So what's going on,
Lee? Why did you tell
us to meet you at this
spot?
[chuckling]
Today there will be
an amazing showdown...
...and we cannot miss
it for the world!
That's...
Kakashi Sensei
and Guy Sensei!
So they're...
Precisely!
A fierce face-off between
Guy Sensei and his eternal
rival Kakashi Sensei!
You do not want to
miss this contest!
Guy Sensei's rival
is Kakashi Sensei.
All right...
Now, let's do
this, Kakashi!
Come on, Guy, not
today. I mean, you've
got a cold!
Please, this is just
a sniffle! Youth waits
for no man!
Let's Rock!
You're too old to still
be going on about youth,
you know.
Excuse me?! It's
about how young at
heart you are!
Ahh-choo!
Sorry.
Kakashi Sensei got
the drop on him!
Oh no! That's
the Tiger Seal!
A fire style jutsu?!
Is he going to use
that at point blank
range?!
Leaf Village Secret
Finger Jutsu!
A Thousand Years
of Death!
[screaming]
Wow! He just poked
him in the butt!
Boy, that had
to hurt.
Oh no! Not Guy Sensei!
You've still got
a ways to go.
[gasp]
Well, I guess I win
this round. If I were
you, I'd wait until
you're over that cold
before you- Huh?
Quick, Kakashi.
I'm hurt real bad.
Call me a doctor.
Hmm, maybe I shouldn't
be poking thirty-year
old men in the butt...
That defeat ought to
cool Guy Sensei down
for a while.
We're really lucky that
Kakashi Sensei is around
to bring him back down
to earth.
Guy Sensei can't win,
but he won't stop.
That is not true!
He can win!
I used to be an underachiever
like you, but now I have a
winning record against the
genius Kakashi!
And my own
popcorn maker!
Diligence and hard work
made Guy Sensei the
equal of Kakashi Sensei!
You've still got
a ways to go.
Agh! What am I thinking?!
I know that Guy Sensei has
beaten Kakashi Sensei
plenty of times before!
Like that one time...
Lee!
Eat these for a hundred
times more energy!
[groaning]
You've still got
a ways to go.
Okay, bad example.
But still, Guy Sensei
has that hot-blooded
passion that Kakashi
Sensei lacks!
You're right, but all
the girls sure love
that cool attitude
Kakashi Sensei has.
Kakashi! Kakashi!
You've still got
a ways to go.
Agh!
Maybe Guy Sensei is
not as good as I
thought!
It's not a big deal!
Kakashi Sensei is just
a really incredible man!
They call him the Copy Ninja
because he's copied over a
thousand jutsu with his
Sharingan!
Oh, but, uh...
Guy Sensei's a
quick learner, too!
Tenten, I must stop
being so soft!
Huh?
I will follow in Kakashi
Sensei's footsteps 'till
one day I am strong enough
to have my own
kunoichi cheerleaders!
That's what your
concerned about?!
But first, I must
master that jutsu!
Neji!
Forget it!
Fine, then I will just
have to train alone!
Come on, that's the
jutsu you're learning?
Our first mission with
Kakashi Sensei, and he's
even tardier than the
rumors would suggest.
And come to think
of it, Lee's late,
too.
Sorry about that!
What?! You're a copy
of the Copy Ninja?!
This is the best way
for me to learn from
Kakashi Sensei.
So you're literally
trying to mold yourself
in his image?
What happened to
your jumpsuit?
We are on a break...
If we take too long to
get going, the enemy will
escape. We'll just have to
leave without Kakashi Sensei.
Our mission is to
capture a group
of rogue ninja.
They've all escaped being
brought to justice numerous
times before now.
We need to proceed carefully
and take them by surprise.
But...
They're the ones
doing the surprising!
But with me here you
have no chance of
defeating us!
You're either brave
or stupid. You're
outnumbered four to
one!
Of course I am. I am the
Copy Ninja who has copied
over a thousand jutsu,
Kakashi Hatake!
He's taking this whole
role-playing thing way
too seriously!
If you expect us to believe
that, you're even dumber
than you look. Show us your
Sharingan, Kakashi!
This is not good!
They're calling his
bluff! Lee doesn't
have-
Sharingan!
What's that?!
Relax, Tenten! They've
been making Sharingan
contacts forever. The
ultimate eyes are no
longer a dream!
Look!
Byaku-Sharingan!
Aw, come on!
Not you too!
You're definitely an
impostor! You're much
too worked up to be the
cool, collected Kakashi!
Agh!
I cannot believe they
saw through my terrible
impression!
What did you think
would happen?! Face it,
they've already figured
it out!
I have no choice
but to use the move!
Wait, I know
that stance...
Behold, the results of
my training to be like
Kakashi Sensei!
A Thousand Years
of Death!
[gasp]
[chuckling]
I've been hit by
that before, so I
come prepared!
An iron plate?! This
is unbelievable!
This whole fight's
unbelievable!
I've battled a Leaf
ninja who used that
same attack before.
That ninja was Kakashi's
father! They called him
the White Fang of the
Leaf's because of the
bite of his Thousand
Years of Death attack!
No, they didn't!
Sorry, kid.
Get him!
On it!
Oh, no! Come on,
Neji, we gotta help!
I can't!
Huh?
These contacts are
making my eyes sting!
Seriously! Now you
decide to get dry eye!
I am doomed!
[gasp]
Guy Sensei?
If you even think of
laying a hand on my
students...
You'll pay the price!
It looks like you're
paying the price, Sensei!
Kakashi Sensei, is
Guy Sensei okay?!
Nope.
But he was so worried
about you that he
rushed off anyway.
Huh?!
Like you, Guy started out
as a hopeless case, with
no talent as a ninja.
But he still challenged
me over and over.
I believe that through
his actions, Guy is always
trying to reveal to you...
...the path that
you should follow.
Ahhh!
And that's the same
kind of jumpsuit
that I wear!
Thank you! They
are so cool!
You wear those, and
someday you'll be as
strong as I am.
Guy Sensei does so much
for me, and I had the
nerve to imitate Kakashi
Sensei instead!
Guy Sensei! It is you!
You are definitely the
best!
[chuckle]
Now! Kakashi, Lee!
It's time to get
serious!
Yeah.
Right!
[gasps]
Don't be scared! We're
completely shielded
from that attack!
Oh, yeah?
What?!
Three Thousand
Years of Death!
Noooooo!
Guy Sensei! I am so
sorry! I lost sight
of what is truly
important!
Lee, you don't have
to say another word.
Guy Sensei!
[crying laugh]
You've still got
a ways to go...
Maybe from your point
of view Guy Sensei
comes up short, but to
me, there is no one who
is greater! And I will
stick by him forever!
Huh?
What are you talking
about, Lee?
About what Kakashi
Sensei just said!
No, no, you've
got it all wrong.
I just meant that my
Thousand Years of Death
still doesn't have quite
the bite that my father's
version did.
Ogh!
Then, you mean...
I've long acknowledged
Guy as my rival.
That's right! And I still
have more wins than you
under my belt, by the way.
Now that is our
Guy Sensei!
In the end, things went
back to normal between
Lee and Guy Sensei. Or
as normal as they get...
Together they redoubled
their efforts, hoping to
find even greater strength.
Would you please work
on a different attack?!
Neji, what kind of
underpants do you
wear to a fight?
I'm not telling!
Aw...
On the next episode:
"I'm Going to Teach
Konohamaru Kempo" and
"I Save My Lucky Undies
for Physicals!"
Ah, I see. We'd
better ask Tenten, too
Oh, I wear- Wait,
I'm not going to
tell you that!
But it is important
for the next episode!
Then why don't you
go ask Sakura!
I could never ask
Sakura such a shameless
question!
Well, then don't
ask me, either!