(Narrator)
March 14th is finally
here, White Day!
(nervous) The friend's
chocolate I got on
Valentine's Day from
Sakura...
(Narrator)
A month ago, and he
still hasn't eaten it.
I wonder if it
really was just
a gesture of
friendship...
No, I can tell. It
appears to be just
a nice gesture...
But there is the
faint scent of love
melted into it!
(Narrator)
In case you didn't already
know, White Day is another
big day for romance--
(Narrator)
Where all the boys who were
confessed to on Valentine's
day give their answer.
And on this White Day,
I must answer Sakura's
bold confession of love!
And what is my
response-!? I say...
YESSSS!!!!!
(Narrator)
Didn't see that
coming..!
"The Alliance to
Destroy White Day"
[crowd chatter]
(Lee)
What on Earth!?
What in the world
happened here!?
Argh! I thought this
white chocolate looked
a little dark, but it
is way worse than that!
--This is dried
fish eggs!!
And that's not even the
half of it! The cookies
got switched with the
pickles--
--the biscuits with dried
radishes, the baumkuchen
cake with fish rolls...
--and the marshmallows
with freeze-dried tofu!
All the sweets have
been switched out!
This is terrible!
White Day is tomorrow!
What sort of heartless
maniac would commit such
a dastardly deed!?
[evil laugh] We've
done it! This is sure
to ruin White Day...
(Tenten)
You wanna find
the culprit..?
Indeed I do. Otherwise,
I will not be able to
properly express myself
on White Day.
Think about it, Tenten!
Even if they were just
token gestures, you would
be upset if you did not
get anything!
Why are they
automatically
"token gestures!?"
Never mind! We need to
take back White Day,
and we need to do it
NOW!
All of the White Day
candy was stolen from
the store--
--and the decorations
were defaces and
dyed black--!
There must be a clue
hidden in there
somewhere! Any ideas?
That's not really much
to go on, you know.
Wait! I just thought
of something...
[gasp]
What business do
you have with me!
I need to ask you a few
questions regarding the
White Day candy theft,
if you do not mind.
Huh!? Come on!
You don't suspect
Shino, do you!?
I think we can safely
profile our criminal as
having a sweet tooth,
as well as...
...an affinity
for black!
The only groups of
people who fit that
description are those in
their teens and twenties!
...as well as those
in their thirties
and forties!
That doesn't
really narrow
it down...
And-- rhinoceros
beetles!!
rhinoceros
beetles!?
Those things love sugar
and are black as midnight
for their whole lives.
Pretty clever, huh?
That's ridiculous!
There's no way the
culprits were a
bunch of bugs!
Do not resist! Hand
over the beetles if
you know what is
good for you...!
I'm afraid I cannot do
that. It is because...
..they've been in
hibernation since
last month!
[horrified gasp]
If Shino's rhinoceros
beetles have the alibi
of hibernation...
...then there must
be another gang of
them out there
somewhere who did it!
What do you say we just
move on and drop the
beetle thing already?
(Mr. Teuchi)
Here! Enjoy!
Huh!?
What is this?
Marshmallows?
Grrr...
Have you lost your
mind, Mr. Teuchi!?
S-sorry... I just
had too many of them!
[groan] This is starting to
be a drag. I've gotta think
of a way to smooth this over
before they get suspicious.
(Narrator)
Well, what do you know?
It looks like we've found
out three culprits!
Ah ha ha! Now
I get it!
[gasps]
[grunt]
You finally finished
creating your new
menu! Am I right?
Oh! You noticed, huh?
[relieved sigh]
What a drag..!
[nom nom]
[big gasp]
Choji! Where did
you get all of
those cookies!?
Oh, these? Shikamaru
gave them to me!
Huh!?
Shikamaru...!
I had no choice! There's
no way I could eat them
all myself. There's just
too many!
Then that means...
Shikamaru...
[nervous gasps]
...must have learned
how to bake cookies!
Wow! I never would
have expected that
lazy bum to have such
a demanding hobby!
What a surprise!
[relieved sighs]
I thought we were
busted there, for a
minute. So, how are
things looking?
Pretty good.
I took the famous "White
Lover's Snowcaps" imported
from our friends up north,
and boiled them in soy sauce.
...Thusly, I turned them
into a brand new product.
Introducing "Black
Lover's Snowcarps!"
Ohh!
I'd say our plan to
destroy white day
turned out to be a
great success!
So that is
your scheme!
[gasps]
What are you doing here,
Lee? How did you find us!?
I just happened
across this place
while searching for
Rhino Beetles!
Still looking for
beetles in March
on a hunch..?
You aren't to
be underestimated..
So you three were the
ones who stole the
White Day candy and
dyed all of the signage!
Why would you do such
a terrible thing!?
Hmf! As you know, Lady Hinata
is eagerly awaiting a gift
from Naruto in response to
her Valentine's Day present.
But knowing that
insensitive Naruto...
Oh yeah! It's
almost White Day!
I completely forgot
about it this year!
Oh well, whatever.
I'm broke anyway.
Guess I'll skip it
this time around.
And Lady Hinata will be
crushed, devastated!
She'll cry for weeks!
I would rather wipe
White Day completely
off the calendar than
see that happen..!
Same here! I hate
White Day, too!
I just know there'll
be a bunch of lowlifes
who use it as an excuse
to go after my Ayame!
Not one of them
will be worthy
of her..!
I agree with them.
I'd rather there be
no White Day as well.
It's... such a drag.
Whaaaat!?
I cannot believe you
are all trying to ruin
White Day for such
selfish reasons!
You are crushing the hopes and
dreams of eager young girls
everywhere who are waiting for a
response from their Valentines!
Do you not see that?!
If you won't back down,
then I'll just have
to stop you myself!
White Day's nothing more
than a stupid spin-off of
Valentine's Day anyway!
It's a sidekick to
a made-up holiday!
What you are saying
may be true...
...but it is still wrong
of you to make light of
what it might mean to others!
Hmm...
Oh gosh! I'm so
nervous, my knees
are trembling like
crazy!
Do not worry, Tenko!
I am sure you will pass
with flying colors!
Thanks, Leeko! I'm
glad you came with
me. I'm so nervous
about all this!
Alright! Who's next?
Oh! Me! Right
here, I'm coming--
[gasp] Be still my
beating heart! What
a gorgeous girl!
So! Tell me, what's
your name..?
Who me!? Uh...
...No, I am just here
as Tenko's friend.
You're the kind of beauty
we only see once a decade
around here! You'll be a
megastar in no time!
(Lee)
And so! A young lady who
went along with a friend to her
audition caught the eye of the
...talent scout, and
ended up making her own
debut instead..!
Until....
Excuse me! I have an
announcement for all
you wonderful people.
This is it for me.
As of tonight, I
graduate from KHG48.
[disbelieving crowd]
Starting tomorrow,
our new center will
be,,, you, Tenko!
Take a bow!
Wait, you mean--
you mean, me!?
You will be amazing.
Do me proud, okay?
I'm not sure if
I can..!
I've spent all this
time trying to
catch up to you...
How can I ever hope
to push myself without
you here driving me to
be all that I can be!?
YOU IDIOT!
I will not stand for
whining like that!
But, Leeko..?
From now on, you
will be the center.
You have to make the
others chase you now!
Understand?
Hold on. What point was
I trying to make here?
We were talking
about White Day!
Oh, yeah! Right!
So, the point I was
making is not to belittle
something just because it
it considered a spin-off!
As someone from the Hyuga
branch family, I believe that
you should understand that
concept better than anyone!
[gasp] Well... I--
Just because your family
would be considered a
sideshow of the main family
does not make you worth less!
Yes, you're right.
Wait a minute!! Who's
family are you calling
a sideshow!?
Ugh, this is all
such a drag !
(Lee)
"Leaf Women's Weekly?"
Just read it, okay?
Let me see here...
"Give your male friends a token
'friendship' chocolate, &amp; watch
them repay the favor with a high
quality handbag on White Day."
"every girl knows:
accessories beat
chocolate any day!"
What!? Designer
handbags? Accessories?! No
way! Is this for real!?
I'm afraid so, son.
Sorry to break it
to ya...
I see what you
mean now...
I knew you'd get
it. Well done.
Will you join our
side on this, then?
Of course! Let us
combine our strength
and fight together!
-Right! -Right!
(Narrator)
And so, White Day
finally came...
All according to plan.
You said it! This'll
definitely be the most
replaced March 14th ever.
Huh!? What the---
[happy crowd chatter]
What's going
on here!?
But, I thought we
destroyed White Day!
What happened?
Ah, Neji, Shikamaru,
Mr. Teuchi. Welcome!
Lee?! What have
you done here?
We talked about this! I
thought you agreed that
White Day needed to be
eliminated!
Yes, I did! And
it has been! Just
as we discussed
it would.
Then what is
all this!?
It is simple.
I remade it.
You remade it!?
Yes! A brand new,
fully renewed holiday
to replace the old
one:
White Day version 2.0!
Also known as White
Day GX for short!
That acronym makes
no sense at all!
I have done a complete
makeover on the day's
image--
--And now things like the
mullet roe and herring rolls
you planted are the gifts
to give!
It's a surprisingly
popular approach!
There are a lot of customers
that prefer saltier foods
like these to sweets
and confections...
...especially since
they go so well with sake!
Candy and other similarly sweet
items have gotten unpopular as
of late as they do not align
with the needs of today's women!
You three opened
my eyes to that!
No way! That wasn't
what we were trying to
say at all, you idiot!
[fighting]
(Narrator)
To all the boys who received
chocolate on Valentine's Day,
(Narrator)
make sure that you return
the favor on White Day.
(Narrator)
Oh. And if you didn't
get anything, don't
sweat it.
(Narrator)
Another staple of
March is Doll's Day.
From the looks of things,
it seems the Leaf Village
held their festival as few
days ago...
Look at that wonderful
display of dolls! It's
simply.. wait, what!?
Huh? The dolls are back
just like they were before.
No matter how many times we
take everything down, the
display's back up again the
next day like nothing happened!
How many days has it
been now? This has happened
every day since the
festival ended, right?
"Clean Up the Dolls!"
No way! Even after they
were all taken down yesterday
the dolls are up again!?
Why are you acting
so surprised about it?
It's happened daily
since the festival.
What a baffling
phenomenon.
It's not a phenomenon,
it's just mean!
March 3rd was over a
week ago and someone's
still putting the dolls out!
It certainly is a
mean thing to do.
I can't believe Leeko
and I hung out so late!
What was I thinking?
I've gotta get back home
and clean up all my dolls
before it's too late!
The 3rd's almost
over..!
Last train for the
Hidden Leaf Village,
number 666, now departing!
All aboard!
Oh no! Wait for me!
What was that story
all about?
You mean you
do not know?
I have heard it said that if you
leave your dolls out on display
too long, you are doomed
to miss the last train home!
Oh, get real! No
one says that!
Is that so? Maybe it
was 'oversleep' then...
It's 'you'll be late!'
Get it right!
(Narrator)
Right! Tenten speaks the truth!
The saying goes that if you
leave your dolls out past March
3rd, you'll be late. As in,
you'll be late in finding a
husband! Not a good thing, i
f
you're looking for one...
What a fascinating
saying! Oh no!
Did you figure
something out?
It is all beginning to
make sense to me now!
It must be because of all
of those dolls being left
out too long that Lady
Tsunade is still single--
ARGHHHH!
Just who do you think
you're calling an old
maid!?
Well, in his defense,
he didn't use those
exact words...
I'm sick enough of those
things being put out year
after year as it is
WITHOU
T that insinuation!
Figure it out
and fix it!!
Easier said than done.
We don't have the first
clue as to what could
be causing it!
Maybe it's just a
bad prank...
A normal display would
be one thing, but that's a
fifty-tiered one created
especially for the Leaf.
If it's a prank, I've no
idea why they're doing it,
nor why they'd go to so
much trouble.
Hmm...
(Thinking)
Yep, he's crazy! That's
the only explanation...
Did you say
something?
Not at all! So, uh,
are we doing it again
tonight Lord Orochimaru?
Of course we are!
By repeatedly leaving the
dolls out, day after day,
year after year--
--we'll turn the Leaf
into a village of old,
unmarried spinsters! No
one left to carry on!
(Thinking)
Another overly elaborate,
yet petty plot...
(Narrator)
Oh, of course. Who else
would be causing this
much trouble but these two?
(Narrator)
Is there nothing they
won't stoop to?
(singing) The Emperor
and the Empress having
a staring contest...
...which of the two
will win? We won't
know until they begin!
Hm...?
Wow, I didn't know
they made dolls this
big.
Aghhhhhhh!
Lord Orochimaru,
what's wrong with you?
The Emperor doll turned
and smiled like this!
It's alive! I'm
telling you! Take
a look!
Doesn't look alive
to me...
...in fact, the
imperial dolls always
look really calm.
No way! I could have
sworn it looked at me!
Let's stop wasting
time and finish up
already!
Hi there! Call me
'Lee!' Blllaahhh!
Ahhhhhhh!
Play with me!
No! Get away!
Play with--
Ugh! Will you please
stop screwing around
already!?
Sorry about that.
I totally became the
doll for a moment. I
was possessed by its soul!
Stop with the
scary stories, too!
Wha? Lee? When did
you two sneak in here?
And why am I dressed
as one of the 5 male
musicians?
I should obviously
be the Empress!
Sorry, that role was
already taken before
you arrived.
By whom!?
By me.
Okay, why is
Neji the Empress?
Ha ha! Aw, Tenten,
that is so very cute
of you.
Do not worry! I have
another outfit that
I think you will like
much better!
(Lee)
Tonight, after you
change, you will be
the princess!
[blush] Oh! Thanks
so much...
Wait! What are you
trying to pull!?
Hey! Think we can
get back to me now?
To think you would re-display
all the carefully cleaned up
dolls in a nefarious plot to
ruin women's chances of marriage
We won't let you
get away with this!
[laughter] It would appear
that they've left us with
no choice but to use force.
Bring it on,
you fiend!
Let's go, Kabuto!
Right, Lord Orochimaru!
(Thinking)
Finally, an
actual fight!
Tenten! Neji! Be
ready for anything!
You got it!
Hmf!
[growling]
[growl back]
What!?
Get back here!
I'll show you! I'll
put all the dolls
back up by force!
Oh yeah? Then I will clean
them all up by force!
What!?
So that's what he
meant by 'force?'
How long are we
gonna keep doing this!?
Probably until one
side passes out from
lack of energy...
It will go on forever
at this rate! I need
to use that move!
What special move are
you planning this time!?
Leaf Ninja Art:
Every Other Step!
Are you kidding!?
Grade schoolers can
do that!
Hm, a fearsome move,
I admit. But overuse
will leave your legs
sore later..!
Don't take his stupid
move seriously..!
Time for my trump card!
Summoning Jutsu: Escalator!
[gasps]
You lose!
This time I am
the victor!
Ah, too easy,
too easy!
Why didn't you
do this from the
start?
No way!
Ha ha ha! You're
finished...!
Unless you somehow find
an elevator, you cannot
defeat my escalator!
And even if you did,
it would be useless!
Accept your defeat!
No! And that is
not true! Elevators
go higher and faster!
So naiïve! Look closely,
mister know-it-all. Don't
you see your elevator's
glaring weakness?
What glaring
weakness?!
Sure, elevators can go
up and down quickly and
with little effort---
But you still have
to gather the dolls
manually at the top.
And for the dolls at
the middle it'd be just
as quick to walk from
the bottom!
Ahhh! I never even
considered that!
Victory is mine!!!
Secret Escalator Technique!
Bringing Lots of Dolls to
the Platform All at Once Jutsu!
I am so beyond
sick of this...
We do not stand a chance
of winning at this rate.
How can we hope
to beat the mighty
escalator!?
So, Leeko, tell me.
Have you picked a
high school yet?
No, afraid not. I
am still waffling...
Are you kidding me? You're
more than smart enough to
continue on to this system's
high school, Leeko! What gives?
No way! Get real!
Hidden Leaf High
School is way beyond
my level!
I would never get in!
There is just no way!
Oh.. What about you,
Orochimaru? Any plans?
I, Uh-- already have
the referrals I need to
get into our high school.
Huh? Referrals?
You mean...
You're on an escalator?
Promise you won't
tell everyone yet.
I'd be too awkward.
(Thinking)
This is an escalator
school for Orochimaru?
But she has never out-scored
me once! Not even on the
mock-entrance exams..!
I will not lose! Not
to Orochimaru!
Whoa, really?
So you rose the escalator
and skipped all the
entrance exams...?
Wow, you geniuses are
something else, for sure!
Oh, go on...
Hey! Look! It's Leeko!
You're simply
amazing, Leeko!
I still can't believe that
you skipped a grade and you
get to start out high school
as a sophomore!
What!? Leeko skipped a
grade!? That's like being
on an elevator!
You said it, Orochimaru!
I studied day in and
day out, all so I could
beat you, fair and square!
I wasn't expecting the
"skip a grade" elevator.
Now I'm embarrassed for
being complacent just
because I had an easy
ride on the escalator.
That entire scenario has
absolutely nothing to do
with our battle.
That leaves me
with only one option...
(Tenten)
Yay! The dolls are up!
Hm?
(Orochimaru)
I'm home.
Welcome back,
Orochimaru!
Take a look, it's
the imperial dolls!
Oh, wow! Thanks
so much!
I'm sorry I couldn't
buy you real dolls. I
know that's what you
wanted...
No, no. I know how
hard things have been
for you lately...
You work yourself to
the bone, day and night,
just so you can pay for
my schooling, mom.
I couldn't be more
happy with these.
(Orochimaru)
I promise to take
good care of them.
[teary] Poor
Orochimaru!
I feel terrible!
You did not do all of
this to make the village
women miss their chance at
marriage and happiness--!
--You just did not want
the Dolls Festival to
come to an end..!
(ugly crying)
It's true...!
Heh heh.. fell for
it... hook, line,
and sinker...
What if I offered
to help you out?
How about it?
Huh?
(Orochimaru)
What!? WHAT!? Enough! Why
do I have to get dressed
up, too!?
Because! By becoming one
of the dolls yourself, you
will be able to enjoy this
happy holiday to the fullest!
If that's the case, then
wouldn't it make sense for
me to be the Empress?
What are we even
supposed to be with
these things on our
heads!?
I think we're supposed
to be bales of rice.
Why does every single
stupid episode have
to end like this!?
(Narrator)
You guess it! Orochimaru
has been foiled again!
(Mr. Teuchi)
The next episode is: "Baby-
sitting Guy Sensei" and "Lady
Tsunade's Marriage Interview"
(Mr. Teuchi)
It's about time! Lady Tsunade's
more than old enough for
marriage interviews!
(Tenten)
You could say the same
thing about your daughter Ayame.
(Mr. Teuchi)
That's true, but there simply
isn't a man suitable for my
Ayame, you know?
(Mr. Teuchi)
If a good respectable man came
along that she cared for, she'd
certainly be free to marry him!
(Tenten)
So if she came to you and said
there was a man she wanted to
marry....
I'd obliterate him!
(Tenten)
So you wouldn't let
her marry, you liar!
(Tenten)
Lighten up! You'll be the reason
she's single for the rest of
her life!