It's Autumn, and things are
finally starting to cool off in
the Hidden Leaf Village.
However, it's that time again.
Yes! The Culture Festival!
It looks like the Hokage's
gonna be attending this.
That's gonna make it
all the more fun...
I look forward to this
day every year!
So tell me, are you
enjoying yourself, Sai?
What's wrong? You got a
stomach-ache or something?
Wake up, buddy! You are at the
Culture Festival! You need to
get excited, have fun, you know!
That's a little too excited,
don't you think?
You're right, Lee.
It's fun being the center of
attention. But I'm afraid I'd
never be as good at it as you
are.
[All] Huh?
Hey guys, is Sai
always like that?
Not really. Not that
I've noticed.
Something must be
up with the guy.
Yeah. Maybe he is upset about
something.
"I'm Sai's new Agent!"
I have got it!
Huh? What have you got?
I figured out what
Sai is upset about!
Sai does not really stand out in
any way. That is just his
personality.
But when he sees everyone
focusing on me, he wishes he
could be the center of attention
instead!
That's completely ridiculous!
He doesn't know people only pay
attention to you because you act
like an idiot!
That's possible.
Could he really be that
perceptive?
[Both Girls]
Two more geniuses
weigh in.
Well obviously we are going to
have to find a way to make Sai
the center of attention at this
Cultural Festival!
Yeah!
I have a bad
feeling about this!
Hold it there, Sai!
Your friends have all come here
to help you solve your problem!
Huh?
[Band Playing Music]
Bands are staples of the Culture
Festival! Do well, and you are
sure to stand out!
Are you ready for our next
song?!
[Crowd Cheering]
Huh?
What! What the hell?
Are you serious?
His normal look is kinda plain,
so I used a little makeup to add
some spice!
A little makeup? This is a joke!
He's covered so completely, I
can't even tell it's him!
It is time to rock out!
Hey! Here's how
you rock and roll!
Look at that. Sai is buried
behind those guys.
[Screaming]
They're completely hogging all
the stage-time!
Listen to my hot licks!
I would but my ears are
bleeding!
[Screams]
[Crowd Booing the Stage]
[Painful Grunts]
Where are you going, Sai? We are
just getting started!
Just what is it you think
you're starting?
You fools crashed our stage and
embarrassed us in front of our
fans!
[Gasps]
[Moans]
Apparently we were wrong.
The crowd was not into our
hard-rocking, passionate brand
of music.
Yeah, our material was
over their heads.
You call that music?! It
was nothing but noise!
It was like fingernails
on a chalkboard!
Yeah, you're gonna have to find
some other way to help Sai,
cause this is a menu for
disaster!
A menu for disaster?
Tenten, you are a genius!
Place your orders here,
everybody!
When people want to be social,
they head for a cafe!
That is where the waiters and
waitresses are the centers of
attention!
He is sure to stand out!
I can't argue with that.
You might be right.
What the! Why are they
dressed up like maids?
Alright, Naruto! Show him
how it is done!
Alright!
Huh?
Ahh!
Welcome to the cafe gentlem-
[Gasps] I'm sorry about that!
What a klutz.
The important thing to remember
is the waitresses who work
here are all people who could
not make it as idols.
The plan is simple! I am going
to turn their flaws into
assets...
...and as a result, they will
become popular in spite of
themselves!
If that happens it will
be in spite of you!
Okay, Sai! Time to go for it!
If places like this make you
happy...
I have to assume you lead pretty
pathetic lives.
[Grunting]
Now all of Akihabara
is your enemy!
Look at Sai's face!
That smile is completely
emotionless! It is the same fake
smile you get from fast-food
joints!
How can I help you?
That is not a compliment Sai!
And as a result, he turned
everyone in this place against
you!
Hmm?
We're outta this place!
Right!
Have a nice day.
Hey, you jerks! What's going
on?!
Why are you sitting here
insulting all my customers?!
Uhhh.
There must be a way to use Sai's
natural traits to make him stand
out.
Natural traits...
Tenten, that's it!
[Frightened Screams]
Well, it looks like it worked!
Sai's ghostly paleness and
barely-noticeable presence
turned out to be perfect in
here.
I am glad I thought of it!
This is how you're
helping him stand out?!
[Frightened Screams]
Wait, Naruto, why
are you running?!
But he is still the
center of attention!
I guess that's true but there's
a little problem. Did you
notice?
He's so scary, everyone ran like
crazy to get away!
So you guys are the reason we
have no customers!
We worked so hard! And within
five minutes, you chased
everyone out!
But Konohamaru, I did not mean
to...
[Screams] Don't make excuses!
Get lost!
I don't know why you're going
through all of this. I'd prefer
you leave me alone.
Sai! Hold on a minute, let me
explain!
Do not walk away!
From where I stand, you are just
a lazy person, who will not even
make an effort to try and solve
his own problems!
Are you comfortable with someone
thinking that about you?!
Huh?
To solve a problem, you have to
be willing to charge forward,
confront it, and hit it on it's
head...
...without fear of trepidation!
Hmm.
You're right. That's what I'll
do.
Excellent! That is the
spirit you have to have!
I agree. And as a start, I'd
like to take part in this.
The Hokage's performing the
legend of Momotaro?
Oiiink.
Here you go pal,
have a dumpling.
Oink! Oink!
We've done nothing but butt into
people's business today.
I prefer the term 'slip' in.
All right! I am off to
fight the ogres!
Ahh!
We will be your opponents in
this confrontation!
[Screaming]
No more sneaking around! Look at
us, we're out here on the main
stage!
I'm going off to fight the
ogres!
Don't go too far! You
four are the real ogres!
We were finally able to make it.
Yes.
Countless people sacrificed
themselves so we could get this
far.
You deserve the credit
for being behind all that.
Well met, Momotaro! Huh?
Excuse me, but what are
you guys doing here?
We come from battle, where we
defeated the fake Momotaro.
I see. And you came directly
here to interrupt my play?
That is correct, and
this is for Sai!
Rasengan!
Ahh!
Eight Trigrams Air Palm!
Leaf Hurricane!
[Gasp]
Take em down, Lady Tsunade!
Um, this is so not
Momotaro anymore!
We are not done! We will just
have to take you down with our
secret team super-move!
That's the new move?
It looks powerful!
We are coming for you!
[Screams]
That was so weak!
The main character is still
there, and active!
Huh?
Super Beast Scroll!
[Growls]
Ahh!
What?
Rogue ninjas!
What are they doing here?!
Darn it! They're onto us!
Ahh!
[Growls]
Hmph.
Those rogues infiltrated the
village.
I noticed them while you and the
others were dragging me around.
When I saw they were after Lady
Tsunade, I did as you told me.
I charged forward and hit them
head-on, without fear or
trepidation.
I completely failed to
see they were around.
Excellent job, Sai.
[Crowd Cheering]
Sai. I just want to say, I am
so sorry for calling you lazy
all this time.
I could not have been more
wrong. You really stood out back
there!
Uh, what are you
talking about?
Come on, spill it! We are all
friends! You wanted to be the
center of attention just like me
right?!
Actually, not so much.
I was worried about all the
kinds of trouble you were going
to put me through before we
were finally finished.
Huh?
What? Trouble?
However, I have to say, when it
was all over, it was kind of
fun!
Really, Sai?
[Sniffles]
Hmm?
[Growling]
[Sniffling]
Let me get this straight, Lee!
You put us all through of this
because of your
misunderstanding?!
[Frightened Screams]
Chaaa!
[Screams]
Being the center of attention
isn't always what it's cracked
up to be.
In this case, though,
it introduced our heroes to the
joys of flying.
A reminder for those of you
enjoying the Culture Festival:
Don't forget about the big
after-party on the last night!
Okay, so where should we go
next?
Hey Lee, what's wrong?
I thought I could ignore it, but
I can not. I have to do this
thing!
[All] Huh?
[All] You're talking about the
'Mr. Leaf Village Contest'?
The winner gets two tickets to a
five-star restaurant.
Huh?
Sakura, my dear. Your eyes are
more beautiful than the night
sky.
Oh, Lee.
Hold it!
Naruto?
I'm not letting you take Sakura.
Hmm. So we fight for her.
You got it.
Oh, brother.
Aren't you gonna compete, Neji?
Well, I-
He would enter the 'Miss Leaf
Village Contest!'
Cut it out!
He's right though. With all the
cross-dressing you do, you'd be
a shoo-in for the 'Miss Leaf
Village Contest!'
[Grunting]
What the hell!
You can't talk to me like that!
I'll show you that I'm a better
man than you two will ever be!
Game on!
"Win Lady Tsunade's Heart."
And we're underway with our
first 'Mr Leaf Village' contest.
It's time to welcome and
introduce our contestants.
We have Choji, Neji, Naruto, and
Rock Lee!
Hey, Choji, what are you doing
here?
Well duh, I want
the prize.
The theme for the contest is,
'The Man I'd Like to Date.'
It's time to get started. Good
luck to all the contestants!
The first event of the
competition centers around
fashion.
The question for each of you is:
What would you wear on a first
date?
I think the right answer for a
first date should be casual, yet
stylish.
What is your answer, Choji?
This...
[Applause]
Very nice. Not bad at all.
Well I would hope so. I spent a
week trying to find the perfect
XXL sized outfit!
You went through
a lot of work.
Next up is Neji!
I'm not a slave to the
latest fashion trends.
It's so non-trendy, it's
completely traditional!
What do you say,
Lady Tsunade?
I think he'd be more at home in
a kimono than a hakama...
[Sigh] Not again.
It's your turn now, Naruto.
My research tells me 'natural'
is the right way to go on a
first date!
[Crowd Screaming]
That's not the kind of natural
you want to go with here.
Really! This isn't so much
'natural' as it is 'back to
nature.'
It would work better if his
body wasn't so scrawny.
This is scrawny!?
The last contestant
is Rock Lee.
Huh?
On a first date, the way to
impress the person you're seeing
is to wear a leggy ant outfit!
It's not 'leggy ant!'
The word is 'elegant!'
Now I get it, it was
a bad pun.
Looks like everyone except Choji
ended up as the butt of a joke.
[Sigh] My butt is no joke!
Next category is the pick-up
line! Guys, how do you ask a
girl out so that she can't help
but say 'Okay?'
You'll be practicing on Lady
Tsunade herself!
Wanna check this place
out with me?
It's a famous bakery, that
offers all-you-can-eat cake!
That was a well-played move!
Choji's banking on the fact that
most girls love a sweet treat!
Sounds great.
Wow, I figured Choji would
suggest getting beef barbeque.
You're not that far off,
actually. His first instinct was
to buy all-you-can-eat barbeque
tickets.
But then I started
thinking about it...
First, I entered a
talent contest.
Wait! You've gone off-track!
What does any of this have to do
with food?!
I had my debut, got popular, and
then got the street in front of
the BBQ place closed off for one
of my shows.
You did a surprise concert?
Since the restaurant couldn't
get supplies, they had to close
for a day.
And Choji had no choice but
to go to the bakery next door,
instead.
I guess this is how you win when
you have an I.Q. of two hundred.
The next one up is Neji!
Please accept these.
Neji decides to go for a direct
strike!
What a beautiful bouquet! Thank
you very much, young man.
Yes. I decided to purchase one
rose for each year of your age.
Hmph.
There are a grand total-
Do not finish that sentence!
Hold it! Forget all these petty
games, you guys!
All you really have to do is
look at her straight in the
eyes!
Let's get together this
Sunday...
You and I, uh...
Forget it. I can't get into it
when it's just you, Granny
Tsunade. With all those wrinkles
under your eyes.
Hmph.
You're supposed to look into her
eyes, not under them!
That is terrible, Naruto!
Hmph! I will show you how to get
a woman to say yes!
Lady Tsunade, will you train
with me on your next day off?
I do not care if you are
fifty-four and have a face full
of wrinkles!
As two single people, we can
overcome the age gap with enough
hard work! That is certain!
All we have to do is-Ahh!
Stop talking, Lee!
You're killing her!
[Gasp] I am sorry Lady Tsunade!
You didn't get an 'OK' to your
proposal, you got a 'KO!'
Forgive me, my Lady.
I think it's time for a
ten-minute break.
Tell me something. Were you
serious back there, Lee?
That whole effort was
horrendous!
Yes, I know. But believe me, I
am trying to give it my all!
I will never be Mr. Leaf
Village! Never! Ever! [Crying]
Lee...
[Grunting]
What kind of a man gives up, and
sits there crying?
You have to find a way to hang
tough! If you don't you will
never be able to date Sakura!
[Gasp] You are right!
You are so wise! That
was awesome! [Crying]
Don't get snot on me!
Get away from me!
I didn't do anything!
Leave me alone!
Tenten!
So gross!
The final event of the
competition is 'Confessions.'
It's the end of the first date.
Admit how you really feel, and
win the woman's heart.
I'm the one you're going to be
confessing to.
We'll begin this round with
Choji. You're up first.
Right!
[Munching]
Um, I know this is gonna sound
cheesy, but would you
consider...
Huh!
Would you eat barbeque with me
for the rest of your life, every
day?!
[Gasp] You stink!
Oh no! A blast of bad breath
ruins everything at the critical
moment!
You didn't prep anything for him
this time, Shikamaru?
'Fraid not. It was too
much of a drag.
Everything you did for him
before was more of a drag!
Does this mean I don't get the
restaurant tickets?
Hmph! For starters, you'd have
to be a lot more romantic.
You try, Neji!
We need to talk.
Go ahead.
Let me ask. Would you
be mine forever?
Yes!
In that case, there's something
important you have to do to
become part of the Hyuga Clan.
I made a quick mock-up, to
demonstrate.
Huh?
Take a look.
Uh.
She has to have
plastic surgery?!
Everyone in his clan does
have the same features.
Is that a bad thing?
Well it doesn't make a good
argument, for a relationship.
Let's see how you do, Naruto.
Well I've never had a girl over
to my pad before, so I was kinda
hoping...
You know, maybe we could...
Hmm. Have you ever cleaned this
place? Let's start now by wiping
down the table with this dust
rag.
That's not a rag. It's just a
dirty sock.
Ew, gross. I can't stay here!
Come on, now! If you really love
someone, you shouldn't worry
about a little dirt!
[Laughing] How naive of you,
Naruto! You have no clue
regarding priorities.
The most important thing to
do in this situation is to
support the woman's
feelings. No matter what!
What are you doing
out there?
Tenten told me to come chase
after you, and stick to my guns!
Did she say stick
to the window?
I swear I will stick by you,
and love you every day!
Yuck! Disgusting!
Girls hate clingy guys Lee!
Hmph.
Hmm.
We'll just have the Lady pick a
winner from among the four of
us!
Sounds good.
Fine by me!
[All] Lady Tsunade!
[All] Will you please!
[All] Go out!
[All] With me!!!
Ahh!
[Heavy Breathing]
You idiots!
Huh?
I can't turn my back for one
minute! What have you done to
Lady Tsunade?!
[Screams]
Talk to me m'lady.
I'm alright.
What a relief!
It is time for the results of
the contest!
Mr. Leaf Village has been
chosen!
It's mister...
...Tenten, everyone!
W-w-what are you saying? It's
me? That can't be right!
After all she's done to protect
me, I would definitely rather be
dating Tenten!
And so, I am awarding her two
tickets to the Heaven's Doorstep
restaurant!
Come and get your prize!
But, this is so weird.
[Crowd Cheering]
[Screaming]
And as for you four...
I've been giving it some
careful thought, and finally
decided I have the perfect prize
for you...
And it's my fists!
[Screams]
And by a weird coincidence, it
turned out that Lee and his
friends ended up at heaven's
doorstep as well!
The next episode is entitled
"Gaara's First Date," and "A
Gift From Orochimaru!"
Wasn't Gaara just here? I mean,
is it okay for him to leave his
village so often?
The Sand Village has it rough,
too. They just set up his new
work visa.
Work visa? Are you saying
he's here on a mission?
No, there's nothing out there
but desert. Maybe he's here to
earn money to send back to his
village?
The Kazekage working abroad?!
You're way out of line buddy!