Happy New Year, everyone!
Out with the old, in with
the new! From Rock Lee and
all of us,
We wish you another
great year!
"A New Year's
Escape Clause."
Now then, as we all now,
the best part of a kid's
New Year's celebration is
always the cash presents!
But what about
the adults?
[sigh]
What's the matter,
Lady Tsunade?
The year's off
to a bad start.
I had my traditional year-
end game night with friends.
The company was great, but
I lost. Big time.
Yes! I nailed it!
Naruto, Sakura, and
Kakashi. I have a full
Team Kakashi house!
Are you kidding?!
I'm doomed!
There's nothing left
in my wallet but some
lonely moths.
This happens to
you every year...
[gasp]
Hurry! Hide!
Yeah, so anyway, how
much did you get,
Bushy-Brow?
Actually, I am not
sure why, but...
Guy Sensei! I wanted
to wish you a Happy
New Year!
Oh! Sorry, kids! My son,
Guy, he, uh, he isn't home
right now!
I'm a bit too old and
sick to greet you outside!
[laughing]
You don't want
to catch this!
So I have yet to
receive my present
this year.
Bushier-brow Sensei,
too? Kakashi Sensei and
the old man at Ichiraku
are also gone.
It seems a bit too
convenient to me that
all of them are busy
somewhere else!
You don't say? I'll
go one step further
and state they're
clearly avoiding us.
It's definitely too
quiet, considering the
usual New Year's
celebration.
For now, we will just
have to keep our fingers
crossed that the adults
come back soon, and
that each one of them
has got our money.
Argh! Those kids?!
Don't they realize their
Hokage's' constantly on the
brink of financial ruin?
You're blowing it out of
proportion. I wouldn't
call losing a few games
"financial ruin".
If I have to give them
cash presents, the
economy will completely
collapse!
Lady Tsunade, the only
thing collapsing around
here is your faulty logic.
And even if I were
to be honest about
it...
You can not get us
presents because you are
strapped for cash? What
a cop out!
Lame. Oldest excuse
in the book.
How shameful. You're
the Hokage. Get your
priorities straight!
I'm doomed! My
reputation as
Hokage is doomed!
Excuse me,
Lady Tsunade?
Oh no, it's Lee. He
and his buddies are
here to shake me down.
Shizune, quick! Make
something up! Get
them out of here!
Uh, seriously?
Good day to you!
And a Happy New
Year!
Oh! Thank you! A-And
the same to all of you!
Is Lady Tsunade
in, by any chance?
Uh, no! She's out
of the office, I'm
afraid!
Wow! Her, as well!
It's like the adults
vanished into thin air.
What a pity. And after
all the trouble we went
through planning the big
party.
Big Party?
Yes. We thought the
village was a bit too
quiet, you see, so we
wanted to throw a party
and get people in
the holiday spirit.
But we also knew a regular
old party wouldn't be enough
to get everyone to come!
So as the main attraction,
we have created a little
something we like to call, the
Ultra-Serious Game of Life!
Did he say the Ultra-
Serious Game of Life?
We wanted to get Lady
Tsunade's permission for
it, but if she's not here...
...Then I suppose we'll
just have to cancel it.
I like the idea of a "Get
out of giving presents"
free card as a prize for
first place.
That's a brilliant idea!
Everyone in the village
will be ecstatic!
She approves! It's so
obvious she just wants
the "Get out of presents
free" card!
Start setting things
up! I can't wait for
this shindig!
Right!
[chattering]
Are- Are you sure about
all of this, Lady Tsunade!
[laughing]
Of course. Now I can
keep my cash without
tarnishing my reputation.
Ooh, what a wonderful
idea. It's brilliant.
And what a wonderful
and brilliant attitude
you have.
That reminds me, everyone
else is hiding out and
laying low, right?
Yes, but once word gets
out about this party, who
knows how they'll react.
That's why you need to
play, too, Shizune. I
want you working behind
the scenes to help me out.
You do? Uh, okay.
If you insist...
And with that...
I'd say I have this
game in the bag!
It's supposed to be a
big event, but will
anyone even show up
on New Year's Day?
They did! All these pathetic
people were lured in just for
a chance at getting out of
giving presents!
What cheapskates!
Welcome! It is now time
to begin the first annual
"Mega Ultra-Serious Game
of Life!"
We have got a wonderful
group of pure-hearted
adults competing today.
As a result, we have
modified the Game of Life
to be more contestant-age
appropriate.
Alongside me on color
commentary is Tenten
Straightman!
I'm not the straight
man, okay?!
Anyway, if you ask me,
this is going to be more
like a war, considering
the age of the competitors
and the contents of
the game today.
Nice, Lee! This was a
fantastic idea! I had
plans, but I couldn't
abandon my brilliant pupil!
Yeah, right! What a
liar. All he cares about
is winning first place.
Ah, so if we win, we
don't have to give the
kids presents? I had
no idea.
You're totally lying!
Don't try to fool us!
Damn it all! I didn't
expect them to show up!
Clearly not, it
would seem...
Ready, start!
First up is Teuchi!
He rolls the die!
Hnh?
Ayame? What're
you doing here?
Well, uh... There's
someone I want to
introduce you to, Dad.
It's a holiday! Who
could you possibly-
You wouldn't consider
it if it were any
other day!
Oh, foolish girl. You're
supposed to spend this day
with your family! I don't
wanna meet some guy I
don't know from a bum
on the street!
A bum on the street?
You jerk!
Teuchi has a fight with
his daughter on New
Year's Day! He loses
a turn!
Wait a minute! This
is what "Ultra-Serious
Game of Life" means?!
Agh! Good! Now's
my chance!
Huh? What are you
guys doing here?
[laughing]
Listen, Kakashi Sensei, I'd
never have accomplished
as much as I have without
your help.
The New Year is a reminder
for us to take a moment to
tell you how grateful we are.
Y-You guys...
Receive words of thanks
from your students. Nice
one! Roll again!
Heh!
Sorry, Guy. I'm
leaving you behind.
Wha- Who're-
Mr. Kakashi, look! Why
don't you date this
girl? She's such a
lovely, nice, sweet lady!
I, um...
Sorry, ma'am.
Someone tell me why
I'm still doing this?!
Oh no! That classic scenario
where you are awkwardly
accosted by a nosy spinster
neighbor on the way
back to your house!
Kakashi loses a turn!
Since when is that
a classic scenario?
Finally, the time has
come! My turn!
What's my dream, you
ask? My dream is to turn
my student into a splendid
ninja... No more beer.
Guy Sensei drinks way too
much at a party with his
friends, passes out, does
not make it home for
New Year's Day, and
loses three turns.
That's gotta hurt!
Guy Sensei's whole
existence hurts! It's
just so painful!
My turn! I have to
win at all costs!
Oh!
Huh?
Maybe you're old enough
that you don't care about
marriage anymore, but your
mom's almost eighty.
Have you thought
about her?
Won't you at least think
about a woman's happiness
one more time? For your
family?
O-Okay...
Oh, the pain of regret! Get
lectured by one's parents
on the meaning of happiness,
lose four turns!
The themes in this game
are getting way too
heavy! Cut it out!
Dad, this is my boyfriend.
He doesn't have a job right
now...
...but he's aiming to
get into a visual kei
band! Isn't that cool!
Better for a man to chase
his dreams than to be bogged
down behind a desk. Am
I right, Dad?
Don't you dare call
me "Dad" you slacker!
My goodness! It is
pure carnage over here!
With that, you
lose five turns!
They're still on
that subject?!
Only Yamato has managed to
make it through the game
area unscathed. This will
be a sight!
After all this time, will
we finally hear his voice
in a victory interview?
That's a sound,
not a sight!
Oh no! The powers that be
have decided Yamato will
have no speaking parts
for another year!
The shock is so great
he is eliminated outright!
What is this?! It's not
even the Game of Life
anymore...
Just who will emerge
from the chaos?!
Kakashi? Guy Sensei?
Teuchi, maybe?
Out in front, ignoring
the urgings of her parents
to marry despite her age,
it is Lady Tsunade!
Stop it! We don't
need that kind of
analysis!
I don't care! Even if I'm
hurt, even if I'll never
find true happiness,
I will overcome the
challenge before me
right now! Bring it on!
Put on expensive facial
products given to you by
an underling who went on
vacation! Advance
three spaces!
Get winning numbers from
an underling's New Year's
card! Advance three spaces!
Go, Lady Tsunade!
You can do it!
We believe in you,
Lady Tsunade!
Almost there!
That's right...
I'd forgotten what wonderful
girls my subordinates are
So supportive and kind.
And here I am trying
to avoid giving them
gifts...
Still...I'm sorry,
everyone!
Lady Tsunade closes
in on the goal!
[gasp]
Come to realize how grateful
you are for the support of
your students and subordinates,
Trade places with the
person in last place?
Uhhh...
What?!
Shizune wins in spectacular
fashion! Her prize is the
coveted "Get out of giving
presents free" card!
Sorry about that,
Lady Tsunade.
And so, the adults of the
Leaf Village learned that
there's just no getting out
of giving kids their
New Year's money.
As the New Year commences, we
resolve to better ourselves,
and in doing so, feel better
about ourselves.
[screaming]
I will take Sakura on
a date to Shinobiland!
Huh?
I will take Sakura on
a date to Shinobiland!
[screaming]
That's enough!
It's a new year. Stop
fighting already! We're
supposed to be getting
a fresh start on things!
Fish for sea beam on the
channel with Naruto.
Even so, someone still
looks rather uneasy.
"Naruto Under Surveillance!"
Hmm...
Looking at Lady
Hinata's behavior...
It's clear that even in
this year of new beginnings,
she's got Naruto on her mind.
Naruto's a good guy.
There's no denying his
ability and perseverance.
And he's certainly got
guts. But there are still
some things I can't overlook!
Like, he isn't even a
chunnin yet! Plus, he's
a terminal klutz.
And on top of that is the
biggest problem of all!
Naruto's publicly declared
that he likes Sakura!
I really like you!
If somehow, against all
odds, Lady Hinata were
to start going out with
Naruto...
...If things went well
for them, he would
become Naruto Hyuga.
As the future head of the
Hyuga clan, Hinata couldn't
possibly change her name
to-
Stop that!
No love, no money, no
prestige, and above
all, klutzy! Never!
No matter how nice of a
guy he is, I couldn't leave
the Hyuga Clan in his hands
like that! Or can I?
It hurts to even
consider...
What's wrong?
Why the serious
face?
Ah, Miss Ayame from
Ichiraku Ramen...
You don't already
have problems this
year...
Well, no. It's not a
problem yet, anyway.
Oh, yes! In the
Game of Life...
Dad, this is my boyfriend.
He doesn't have a job right
now...
...But he's aiming to
get into a visual kei
band! Isn't that cool!
Better for a man to chase
his dreams than be bogged
down behind a desk. Am I
right, Dad?
Let me ask her.
So, uh...
Let's say that you
had someone you
wanted to marry...
Huh? Where'd that
come from?
And let's say your Dad
objected outright. Just like
in the Game of Life! What
would you feel.
Furious. I'd
loathe him forever!
Hey! What's the matter?
Nothing. Just felt
like I got pierced
by an arrow.
Wait. Hold on
a second!
Does that mean when I
stepped in thinking I
was in the right...
I'm furious. I'd
loathe you forever.
That was how she felt?!
[screaming]
What are some things he
would have to do to make
you not loathe him? What
steps could he take?
I'm talking about Mr.
Teuchi, of course.
Hm... Well, that's easy,
actually. Just have faith
in me, and accept whoever
I had feelings for
that I ended up
bringing home.
But what if the person
you chose was lacking
in certain areas?
Important areas?
One shouldn't be
so judge-y. Nobody's
perfect, right?
And besides, everybody's
got their good points,
don't they?
If he manages to find
those good points and
accept him, then everyone
will be happy!
Find the good points
and then accept them.
Cawppy New Year!
I think we should kick off
the new year with some team-
building sports! Everyone
up for some badminton?
Yeah!
Excuse me, Sakura. Will
you be my badminton
partner?
Back off, Bushy-Brow!
Sakura only needs one
badminton partner, and
that's me!
[growling]
Yeah, I think I'll
sit this one out.
Fine. Then I guess I'm
stuck with Neji or Tenten.
What do you mean
"stuck", you jerk?!
Hmm, who should I
play with then?
Um...I...
Well, I uh.. I..
just... N-Naruto.
Hold it, Naruto!
You will be my
badminton partner!
Neji? Why Naruto?
Yeah, what gives?
Why you being so
pushy?
It doesn't matter what
gives. You're playing
with me and that's
final!
Fine, fine, whatever
you say! Just drop
that stance already!
If I partner with
Naruto...
Hey! Are you okay, Neji?
Sorry...
Then maybe I can
find some of his
good qualities.
Naruto! Neji!
Here it comes!
Whoa!
Keep at it, Naruto!
You can do it!
Hmm, I can see how
Naruto can be appealing
in situations like this
one...
It's like how the fast
kids are always the
popular ones in grade
school.
[cheering]
But fast or not, he's
no lightning bolt,
and never will be.
And speed's not enough
to convince me to leave
the Hyuga estate in his
care.
Uh?!
Well, good morning to
you, Neji! Now that
you're awake, maybe
you can cover me!
Don't cop an attitude with
me, you little jerk! If this
guy marries Lady Hinata...
What the heck?! I told
you to wake me up if
I slept in!
I forgot! I'm so
sorry, dear...
That little hothead
would start bullying
her for sure!
No matter how much she
may loathe me for it,
I'm going to have to
object to their marriage.
Huh?!
What's your problem?!
Do you even want to
play or what?!
[screaming]
Cool your jets,
Naruto. It's just
badminton, after all.
Yes, that's right. It's
just badminton. I can't
actually gauge Naruto's
good qualities with
such a simple game.
Yeah, Naruto.
Play nice, okay?
Play nice?
Play rice...
That's it!
Mochi!
Huh?
I don't get it. Why
are we making mochi
now?
You just cannot get any more
traditional than mochi. This
will really make it feel like
the New Year has begun!
Yeah, that's an
excellent point!
Good idea!
Naruto, I was
wondering if
you'd be-
Wanna be my partner?
Seriously, why do
you keep picking me?
Making mochi.
This should give me
a chance to find his
good points.
Hey, Neji. You okay?
Sure am! I'm ready
when you are.
[grunting]
[screaming]
What are you doing?!
Get in sync with me,
Neji!
Get in sync with you?!
Of all the nerve. If he
started dating Lady
Hinata...
Oh, no! Hold on.
Wait, Naruto!
You slowpoke. Stop
dawdling and keep up.
He'll turn his back on
her! He'll leave her
behind! Perhaps I really
should object, even if
she loathes me for
it?! Decisions...
You move too fast,
Naruto. Take it easy!
It takes two to get
in sync, you know.
That's right.
It takes two...
Yes...
That's it!
Huh?!
Why're we having
another New Year's
party?
To make it feel even
more like the beginning
of a New Year has truly
begun!
Yep, sounds good
to me. Let's have
fun!
Hm?
Excuse me, Naruto. Would
you like a drink? It's
really delicious.
Naruto, old buddy!
Why don't you help
me entertain?!
Again, why me? Why
does it have to be me?!
If the two of us can
work together like this,
I'm sure I'll find some
good points to-
[groaning]
Knock it off already!
What now?!
Every step of the way,
it's just like I thought.
I won't accept anything
more than a platonic
friendship!
Seriously, what is
your problem today,
Neji?
Everything we've done so
far has been your idea.
Why do you keep getting
mad?
Did he say platonic
friendship?
Wait...
Does Neji...
I just don't get it!
What if- What if the
daughter's boyfriend
doesn't have a single
redeeming quality?!
What then?!
Not one? Well, maybe
not to a father...
[gasp]
But if I truly loved
him, then I wouldn't
give up. I'd train
my man to do better
until my dad eventually
accepted him.
Train him to...
Do better...
Naruto!
N-Neji? What's with
the girly outfit?
Look, I don't like it
anymore than you do...
But I must! Not only for
Lady Hinata, but for the
entire the Hyuga clan!
Sic 'em!
[growing]
What the-?! Hey,
wait! Hold on a
second!
Follow me, Naruto.
I'll whip you into
shape!
Whhaaaaat?!
You fool!
You say, "Good Morning,
honey! I love you!"
every time you wake up!
Remember to always
hold hands in a crowd!
And what kind of person
are you if you don't
pick up the tab?!
It's just common sense!
Don't' you faint on me.
We're not done here!
Please, stop this!
Lady Hinata?
Neji, I'm sorry.
I never knew.
Never knew what?
Listen, Lady Hinata!
This is all for-
I know.
You care for him! You
did all this just to
get closer to Naruto,
didn't you?!
Huh?
I understand why you
couldn't tell me, but
I'll show you. I'll get
closer to him than you
could ever dream of!
I won't back down,
you'll see!
Whaaaa?!
And so, Neji learned early
in the year that it's not
a good idea to stick his
nose into other people's
love lives.
The next episode is "An
Endless Nightmare" and
"A Robot from the Future!"
Listen, Neji. I've
come to a conclusion.
What is it,
Lady Hinata?
You and I should compete
fair and square for Naruto's
favor. Shall we agree to
refrain from any backstabbing
or underhanded tactics?
No, really, you've
got it all wrong. I-
Please, hurry! I need you
to sign this contract before
I start hating your guts!
Quickly, quickly, sign it!
Ah! All right! Talk
about an endless
nightmare...