(Narrator)
Well, my friends, another
Setsubun has come and gone.
(Narrator)
Did everyone out there
have fun scattering beans?
(Narrator)
Here in the Hidden Leaf
Village, they have the
same tradition as we do!
It's time, everyone...
for our annual bean-
scattering competition!
This year our
onis are...
...Team Three! Lee,
Neji, and Tenten!
I should have guessed
it would be our team.
Hey, are you saying
there's no way out
of this..?
I say, let us all
give the job everything
we have got!!!
[nasty chuckle]
I did it! I succeeded
in making Lee the oni!
What is the point of
doing so, Lord Orochimaru?
It's quite simple, really.
Once he's been weakened
from being pelted with
beans. I'll be able to swoop
in and finish him off!
Maybe it's just me,
but isn't that
inefficient?
"The Staff Will Eat
the Beans Afterwards"
I'm surprised these
costumes were already
prepared for us...
Not only that, but
they're kinda
embarrassing.
Please do not be
ridiculous! Of all
people, onis do not
get embarrassed.
Excuse me, but
you're a thunder
god, not an oni!
How could that
happen..!?
Huh!?
How could that happen?
How could that happen..?
How bout that?
Look at this!
I had no idea!
A mask comes with
this costume!
Well you're the
only one! We didn't
get anything like
that!
[nasty chuckle]
That's terrific! Now
hurry up and put it on!
What exactly is
happening, my lord?
That, my friend, is a
terrifying mask I prepared
especially for Rock Lee!
What's so
terrifying
about it?
[chuckle]
No question about it!
With this, I will
really be able to get
into character!
[struggling grunts]
[screaming]
Lee? What's
going on..?
It is the mask!
The maaask!
What about
the mask!?
[gags] It stinks
something awful!
[disgusted yells]
Are you sure it's
coming from the mask?
Oooof! Never mind!
You're right! It's
awful..!
Oh yuck! Get
it out of here!
I'm trying to figure
out what's going on
It's not terrifying
because it's cursed
or anything?
[chuckle]
No it's nothing
like that...
The inside surface
has dead fish rubbed
all over it!
No matter what I do,
this mask will not
come off!
That doesn't make
any sense! What's
happening!?
Do you think
it's cursed?
It might as
well be...!
The end result
is the same!
This is crazy! So
if it's not cursed,
what's really
happening here?!
(Orochimaru)
I covered the inside
of the mask with super
sticky double-sided tape!
Huhhh...
Now Lee is stuck with
that stinky mask for
the forseeable future!
He won't be able to
smell straight for
the next six months!
Let us knock this
out of the park!
Alright! Who has
been naughty!?
That's a namahage
demon , not an oni.
[pain grunts]
Naruto!? What do you
think you are doing
up there, you idiot!
That really hurt!
[chuckle]
I'm throwing beans
to ward off the
oni, of course!
[pain grunts]
Throwing handfuls of
beans is what Setsubun's
all about!
So just because I am
an oni, you get to
randomly hit me with
whatever you want!?
Isn't that the
whole point of
being an oni??
Out with the demons
...in with good fortune!
I am not the kind
of oni who will sit
here and take it!
[grunts]
Sorry about that,
Lee! But we're just
following tradition!
[groan] I had no
idea this was such
an unfair process!
Out with the demons..!
...In with
good fortune!
The truth is. they're
not wrong about the
nature of the event.
But they're enjoying
it way too much!
(Tenten)
And while I'm thinking about
it, tell me this: How come
they're only going after Lee?
[chuckle]
Oh, I can answer
that one.
I used a technique that
makes anyone who sees the
mask, want to bombard it
with beans!
Really? You can
do that?
[groan] W-wait a
minute! Time out!
We have no
choice, Lee!
It's time to
retreat..!
This is just the
beginning. Before it's
over, this will be the
Setsubun from hell!
[heavy breaths]
It was close,
but we got away.
A bean!?
Did they catch
us already!?
Do not panic.
Look, it's only
a child!
All demons have to
be... chased out!
Why do I have
to do this!?
He must be from
the outskirts of
town...
Young man... where
are your parents?
They're both
as work...
Aha! Now I see! They are
both too busy with work,
and you had no one at home
to play demon for you!
[cries]
It is okay! Hit me
with every bean you
have in that box!
Okie-dokie! Out
with the demons!
[laughter]
Maybe I should
not have done that.
Thanks a lot,
Mr. Oni!
Well, Lord Orochimaru.
I did as you asked, and
was able to throw a whole
bunch of beans at Lee...
But it didn't really
injure him at all, so
what was the point?
The point is quite
simple, my friend!
I was able to mix my
own boogers in with
those beans!
So now he's covered
in beans AND boogers!
Take that, Lee!
[vomiting]
How is the guy supposed
to be grossed-out if
he has no idea what
you pulled off?
It doesn't matter to
me if he has no idea!
Lord Orochimaru...!
What is that you're
wearing!?
[growling sounds]
[frightened screams]
It's ridiculous! That
outfit's not going to
food them!
It is a tiger!
Where did it
come from!?
Do you think
it's from the
zoo!?
I don't know!
What the heck!? How
can they be scared?
The costume's so
amateurish!
What's this tiger
doing out here anyway?
It looks like he
is trying to tell
us something...
I have been looking
everywhere for you! You
are the spitting image of
my long-lost husband!
This has been very
upsetting to me! I
hope you are finally
ready to come home.
Excuse me?
She's mistaken you
for someone, because
of those pants.
I knew there was
something wrong when
you did not come home
for dinner...
Do not try to deny
it, I would know
those stripes anywhere!
Oh no! This is
made from her
husband's pelt!
Lee...
What are you
gonna do?
The right thing,
of course! Consider
your husband returned!
I can't believe
you are doing this!
[sigh]
I had it figured out right.
I knew he'd take his pants
off eventually, I just had
to push the right button!
So you were after the
kid's pants? You mean
that's what this whole
exercise was about?
Now I just need to get
the villagers out here to
witness this, and he'll be
trapped like a naked rat!
How could that happen?
Hey, the sun's
about to go down.
Being free of that
impersonation has given
me a cool, refreshing
feeling in my lower half.
Ya know what,
you're already
way too free!
We finally found
the onis!
You won't get away
from us again!
What!? Yikes!
There's no escape!
How did they
track us down?
(Lee)
Sakura is with
them!
[embarrassed cry]
Please do not look!
Why do they all have
to be so mean to me?
What did I ever do to
provoke them!?
Is it because I am
an oni? And if so,
are onis this powerless?
That is impossible!
Onis are terrifying
beasts! They cannot
be weak!
I... get it!
[groan]
(Tsunade)
Attention, everyone!
The bean-throwing is
now over!
But I have so
many left in
the box!
Okay! Time
to go home.
Lee!
Are you okay?
I think I am
fine... sort of.
[nasty chuckle]
That's too bad...
Orochimaru!
I've come to finish
you... for good!
[grunts]
[gasps]
It is alright, my
friend. You do not
have to act so evil.
Huh?
What are you
talking about?
It is quite simple
really. I learned
something today,
playing the oni...
I know how
they feel.
What? I beg
you're pardon?
I can see now that
oni truly just want
to make friends and
play with everybody.
For instance...
It is like cats
with mice....
...or monsters
with heroes...
or kaiju with
cities...!
They end up being cast
in the role of villains,
but really, to them, the
fighting is all in good fun.
That is how you
feel, right,
Orochimaru?
I suppose.
You are more than powerful
enough to destroy the village,
but you only try these
petty idiotic schemes.
You really just have
fun tussling with us,
and want to keep doing
so, do you not?
What?! You are out
of your mind. I
refuse to listen
to this dribble!
Prepare to die
Lee! Huh!?
Feel free to come at
me and do your worst,
Orochimaru!
Believe me, it is
perfectly okay,
because today I
am the oni!
Huhhhhh?
Do it!
You get away from me,
you nut case! You're
freaking me outttttt!
(Narrator)
So there you
go, kids.
(Narrator)
Next year, when setsubun comes
around, you might like to find
out how it feels to be the oni!
[panting breaths]
Looks like both of
you are worn out!
That's my cue to hit
the road... bye-bye!
Ah! I did not
expect him to
disappear like
that!
I'm so exhausted.
It's hopeless...
It's alright. This
has been a
particularly long
mission.
I agree. We need
to find somewhere
we can all rest.
"The Raikage is Under Attack"
So that's the Hidden
Cloud Village...
If I'm right, that's the
place where the ninja who
hosts the Eight-Tails
inside his body lives.
Yo yo! Did I hear
somebody call for me?
Killer Bee's my name
and rappin' is
definitely my game!
I see we got us some
ninja from the Leaf!
Are y'all sneakin' around
tryna be a thief?
Gimme the word,
y'all! Fools, ya fools!
Is this some
kind of joke?
I'm tellin' you now,
this ain't no joke!
This is my rap,
slowpoke! Oh yeah!
I have a message for
you new folk! You
can't be hatin' or
you might get smoked!
[groan]
Preach on, rap-
master! I'm down for
some smoked salmon!
I agree completely!
In fact, I would
love some smoked
sausage!
Will you stop
trying to imitate
this guy!?
I'm tellin' ya,
you needs to
chill, babe!
-Ya fool! Ya fool!
What in the world is
going on here? This is
really annoying and now
they're all best friends!
Bee! Drop-kick!
Just where do you
think you're going?
I told you not to
wander around alone!
Uh, y-yes, bro.
(Thinking)
Oh my goodness! That's
the leader of the
village, the Raikage!
All of us have
to be on our
best behavior!
He's so macho,
isn't he?
What kind of training do
you do, Mr. Macho- sir?
Oh! They're so
embarrassing!
Do the two of you want
to feel my wrath!?
-We are very sorry!
Chillax, brother! I'm
here to guard you!
And you know why?
'Cause I don't want
things to be hard on
you! Oh yeah!
Are you crazy!?
I don't need your
protection, you
imbecile!
Excuse me, but why
does your brother
needa guard?
I guess you haven't
heard, have you? Well
here's the skinny...
My bro's in danger,
someone wants him dead!
And this mystery stranger
has got us seein' red!
Oh please, I have
countless enemies
out there.
I've spent my whole
life fighting other
shinobi, and other
villages!
The fact of the matter
is, shinobi are fated
to hate one another.
I do understand.
Hm? What's wrong,
Neji? You look so
mad...
It's nothing.
Nothing at all.
It's something....
(Narrator)
Since Lee and his team were
conveniently in place, they were
assigned to guard the Raikage.
I have to presume you
have many talented shinobi
in your village, right?
You got that right!
Master Bee.
(Bee)
Omoi. Karui.
We were just
wondering what you
were doing, master.
And you, Lord Raikage.
And who are these
people walking with
you? Leaf ninjas?
This is serious! They
could be Master Bee's
new disciples!
If they're any good,
they may end up taking
over my position!!
You've got a pretty
heavy imagination!
He has a tendency
to over-think things.
I Have a feeling you
came here for no
particular reason at all.
And you don't give
things a second though!
Hm? Cloud Style!
Back Slash!
It's a trick move. It
looks like I'm about to
cut you, but I slash
behind me, instead!
Woooow!
You couldn't have
blocked the attack
normally ?
Wait, if you can't see
behind you when you're
cutting....
It re-arranged Lord
Raikage's hair! And
now he has an entirely
different look!
Now I'm doomed! Lord
Raikage's gonna get
really mad, and take
revenge!
I'm gonna give you
an even uglier cut!
So dramatic!
Relax, I know this guy.
Give him a few minutes.
He'll probably decide
he likes the new look.
I haven't looked
this good in years!
So light hearted!
You're all supposed to be
highly trained ninjas. Can't
you try to play it cool?
(Omoi)
Captain Samui!
And Atsui!
How do we know you'll
be effective when it
reallycounts..?
Lee! Prepare to
passionately protect
the Raikage!
Yes, Guy Sensei!
Ready!!!!!
That'll be enough
of that!
This is sweet, sis!
Everyone is fired up!
Why can't everyone
stay cool...
Please don't get so
depressed, Ms. Samui!
Aha! I thought I
smelled trouble.
(Raikage)
Darui! Cee!
The enemy has
infiltrated the
village!
I expect it'll be a
boring job, but we
willfind him!
People around here really
wear their hearts on their
sleeves! Not to mention
their names...
Omoi. Karui. Darui.
And Cee.
That is interesting. I
wonder what our names
would be if we lived here.
Hmm...
Stop it! We're
not going there!
Hm?
Who's hiding back
there? Come out, now!
He's able to create
black lightening?
That's Darui's lightning-
style move, Black Panther!
The previous Raikage
decided to teach Darui, and
Darui alone, the secret
to shaping lightening!
Wow! Incredible!
Lightning Style!
Black Pan--- ties!
Ahhhh!
This is terrible!
He hit his tongue
and Black Panther
became panties!
AARGGHHHHH!
Looks like Lord Raikage is
receiving a critical hit!
Darn it! Now the
intruder's getting
away!
Lightening!
Laser! Support---
Braaaaa!
Oh come on, guys.
That's really pushing
things too far.
Nooooo!
This is becoming
some kind of
disturbing sexy jutsu!
Hm?
I won't let anyone
hurt my brother!
Stand back while I
take care of this
bad mother--!
Did he grow an
octopus tentacle?
The Eight-Tailed Beast
lives inside Master Bee.
...and he's got
complete control
of its power when
he needs it!
Yo, people! I'm the
big Eight-O, and you
don't mess with me,
YO! Yeahhhh!
Hey! You're not supposed
to transform inside the
village!
What's the big deal,
big daddy?
Bee! You idiot!
Turn back to
normal at once!
Walking around the
village in that form
is dang--- AHHHH
Uh oh! I just
nailed my big bro!
Have you gone insane!? We
have to find Lord Raikage
as fast as possible!
Now that he's been
injured, he'll be
defenseless, and easy
prey for the assassin!
Hey, bro, I did mess
up! But at least I had
the courage to fess up!
Ya fool! Ya fool!
[groan] Just being
around these crazies
completely exhausts me!
Let me tell you something,
I feel your pain...!
Huh?
Hold on a second! I
just noticed something.
Did your white-eyed friend
wander off somewhere?
Our village is pretty
big, you know. He might
have gotten himself lost!
He is right! I
just realized,
Neji is gone!
Hm. Let me as, this white-
eyed friend of yours, does
he happen to be... a member
of the Hyuga family?
Yes, actually.
It's possible...
What is possible,
sensei?
I know both you and
Tenten have been
told the story...
...about how the Leaf
and Cloud villages were
at war years ago... and in
the course of that action...
...Neji's father
was killed.
[gasp]
Yes, I remember.
Excuse me?
What are you guys
talking about?
Thirteen years ago, there
was very nearly a war
between our two villages...
...centered around the
Leaf's Hyuga clan and
their Byakugan.
But ultimately...
Neji's father sacrificed
himself to stop the war.
And in the process,
protected both his clan,
and the two villages.
I see now. That gives
your friend Neji more
than enough motive to
go after the Raikage.
You have no
proof of that!
(Darui)
You have to admit
the possibility.
[groan]
(Darui)
And if it's true, we have
to find and confront Neji
as soon as possible!
I finally found him.
Oh no! Are we
too late?
[grunts]
(Tenten)
Wait a minute...
Neji is protecting
the Raikage!
(Lee)
You are right, Tenten!
And the enemy is that rogue
ninja we've been chasing!
(Neji)
He used a very high
level invisibility
technique to escape!
I decided to go off
on my own, to make
sure I wouldn't lose
sight of him!
There's no hiding
from my Byakugan!
But... aren't
you a Hyuga?
I don't get it...
Why would you help
me, considering
our history?
...The fights between
our two families?
...it's because of my
father's last words.
Please pass this
message on to my
son, Neji...
Tell him I chose death
freely.. to protect my
family... my village..
and my son...
...that just for this
one time.. I wanted
to rebel against my
destiny as a Hyuga...
...and at this critical moment
...to choose my own fate.
And that is all
there is...
Lord Raikage, you said
earlier that we shinobi
are fated to hate one
another...
I understand what
you are saying...
but I reject it!
I choose to rebel
against that fate!
Hm?
You aren't getting
away this time!
[grunt]
Yeeeeahhhhhh!
ALright, it is time
for the Lariat!
Why do you want
to use a Lariat?
Woah!
Lookout!
Ahhhh Wait! Whoa!
Just a minute..!
Eight Trigrams
rotation Lariat!
Yeah, he tripped at the
worst time, but he was
able to disguise it as a
new move!
You guys really
came through for
us...
It was nothing...
...but its a good start.
The leaf and Cloud villages
will walk together, toward
a brighter future.
After all, I know two
incredible shinobi who would
do anything to protect both
our villages for their families.
Our villages are
their families...
[small sob]
Your strong dedication sent
shivers up my spine! Now
you've got to come along
with me for some training time!
Ya heart me there,
perfect tool, fool,
ya fool!
No thanks...
Hey, as long as we're
all out here, let's
seize the opportunity!
I say! Go fry me
up some rice, yo!
I am ready to work,
but first I need some
JERK, chicken that is!
Oh boy. This can't
lead to anything good.
(Narrator)
And that's the end of that
chapter for the Cloud Village.
But the team decided to stay
(Narrator)
and train a while. It didn't
take long for them to channel
the spirit...
Are ya ready!? Well
then, let's rock steady!
Let's make it rain,
'cause it's time to
train!
Can someone here
tell me what kind
of training this
is for?!
(Neji)
Next time: "A Fiery Snow-Sculpt
Contest" and "The Battlefield
Called Valentines Day!"
(Neji)
Lee, you had a rough
time with those beans,
huh?
(Lee)
I am all right! The real
victim was neither me,
nor Orochimaru!
(Neji)
What!? I didn't realize
there was a victim!
(Neji)
Fill me in on what
happened! Did someone
get hurt?
(Lee)
Do you not remember that
Orochimaru mixed his boogers
in with the beans?
(Lee)
And the title of the first
half of the show was "The
Staff Will Eat the Beans"..?
(Neji)
Oh no! The poor
staff! How horrible!