(Narrator)
Greetings, everyone!
It's Christmas Day!
(Narrator)
And here in the Hidden Leaf
Village, the residents are
celebrating with a big party!
"Christmas Is The Last
Chance For Love"
(Shizune)
Attention, everyone!
I'm sure you're all having
a great time, but let's take
a moment to gather 'round
for the gift exchange!
As you can obviously see, we've
got the presents everyone
brought piled high on stage
under this beautiful tree!
Of course, now the question
is: Who will get which present?
And it's time to get excited
about that answer!
[cheering]
-Time to get serious!
The gift exchange is the
Christmas party's most
anticipated and
compelling activity!
The truth is, the presents
are the main reason people
even come to the party!
And no matter what...
...I am going to take
home Sakura's present!
...I am going to take home
Sakura's present! Ya know!
Oh brother... those
two are impossible!
They always make such
a big deal out of this
event every year!
You're sick of it
too, right, Hinata?
...Huh?
Hinata..? Hello!?
No matter what, I'm gonna
get Naruto's present!
It's coming home
with me, ya know!
Oh wow, Hinata is
completely possessed!
Neji... Help me out
here. Say something,
will you?
I should have figured...
Whatever gift Naruto bought,
it's surely meat for Sakura.
Oh, come on!
Not you too !
If Hinata gets his
present, it will have
absolutely nothing to
do with her...
A cherry "Sakura"
mochi-cake?
This gift was meant
for Sakura! [sob]
Hell no! I cannot
let that happen!
Cut it out, Neji.
I've never heard
of an overprotective
cousin!
I wonder if anyone
wrapped up a big
plate of meat!
Is food the only thing
you and your bone-head
brain can think of!?
This is a pretty
big drag, I
should go home.
Who's stopping you!?
Just get outta here!
[mumbles]
Argh! There are too
many people with
individual agendas!
Lady Tsunade will
explain the rules!
We've set it up so that
each team will be competing
in a survival race--
Each door you see before
you, leads to the room
where the presents are
currently located.
What that means is, each
door leads to the goal, but
there are many obstacles and
traps you'll have to get past.
Whoever gets to the room
first, can pick whichever
gift they like, got it?
Yeah!!!
Alright then, let
the gift exchange
survival race begin!
[eager cheers]
Let's rumble,
Bushy-Brow!
You are on,
my friend!
But I am telling you
now, Sakura's present
is all mine!
Only if you're
able to beat me!
NOT!
And now, we'll see what
happens! The teams have
entered their respective
doors!
We're gonna win this
race for sure, Hinata!
We know how you
feel about Naruto!
Thanks so much,
Shino and Kiba!
(Shizune)
Ladies and gentlemen,
Team 8 makes it to
the first room...
Huh? What is this?
Yeah, it happens every
year. THe whole world's
focused on Christmas...
...and us single
guys are left out
in the cold without
a lot to celebrate.
Well, when you really think
about it, Christmas is really
for the youngsters, wouldn't
you agree, Chief Guy?
I guess so. Let's go
knock back a few down
by the station.
Ooo! That sounds
like a plan!
We'll celebrate the
only way that single
adults know how!
You three wanna come?
[gasps]
What... a polite
offer...
(Shizune)
And there you have it, folks!
The first pothole in the road!
(Shizune)
Team 8 has been trapped by
the camaraderie between two
old bachelors!
Of course, on the other
hand, I should have known
the traps would be like this.
Come on now, Chief
Kakashi... Ms. Hyuga
is still a young
woman...
She's probably going
to spend the night
with her boyfriend.
(Shizune)
A high-pressure situation
with a tinge of sexual
harassment!
(Shizune)
They'll have a hard time
saying 'no' now!
Chief Guy, Chief
Kakashi, Shino and I
will come with you.
[gasp]
Hinata, though, needs to
leave early. She hasn't
been feeling all that well.
Leave them to
us, Hinata.
Yes! You go
on ahead!
Kiba... Shino...
Thank you!
(Shizune)
So noble! So moving! This
is truly what a Jump anime
is all about!
(Shizune)
Ah, and here is Team 10. But
they seem to be missing a member
-What could have happened!?
Wait a minute...
Where's Choji?
You know what? That is
a very good question.
We have a special today,
ladies and gentlemen! Forty
percent off, all you can eat!
The first ten
customers only!
(Shizune)
Why am I not surprised? Choji's
been totally distracted by an
offer for deep-discount chicken!
That idiot! How could
he fall for something
like this?
You go on ahead,
Ino. I can't leave
Choji behind.
(Shizune)
How dramatic! Well, it feels
like it should be dramatic.
(Shizune)
But something's off here.
Not sure what it is...
Oh boy, what a drag.
(Shizune)
Hold on, he's in line
too!? He's not supposed
to be that dumb!
(Shizune)
Let's check in on the
progress of team 7.
[gasps]
Huh? What the?
(Shizune)
Our team has stumbled into
a lonely bachelor's apartment.
(Shizune)
He has no one to celebrate with,
so he's playing some games by
himself on Christmas. So sad.
So, what do you think
we should do?
I'm scared...
(Shizune)
They appear to be
deliberating carefully
over the problem...
(Sakura)
Right hand, Red!
(Shizune)
It seems they've decided that
Sakura & Sai will both stay
behind & keep the boy company
(Shizune)
It's noble, but I have
to say, I do feel sorry
for them.
(Shizune)
Team 3 is lagging behind.
I wonder, have they been
caught in a trap as well?
(Ramen Guy)
Don't just stand there!
Come and sit down...
What is the matter, Mr.
Ichiraku Ramen guy?
Family...
My daughter said she's bringing
her new boyfriend home today.
And I feel so awkward meeting
him, I cant bring myself to
go home!
(Shizune)
It's so hard being a father!
And dealing with a daughter's
boyfriend? Well, that's obstacle
to overcome!
Why exactly does the
trap have to deal
with an obstacle?
This will not do,
my friend. How about
I help you out?
We will meet
him together!
Lee, you don't
really have the time!
We're on a deadline,
you know. We have
to keep moving!
That is so cold,
Neji. Imagine how
you would feel...
...if Hinata announced
she was bringing home a
new boyfriend!
Guh!
Neji! This is the
love of my life!
My new boyfriend!
Let's drown our sorrows
together, pops!
Does this mean you'll
keep me company!?
Thanks a lot!
(Shizune)
Neji's imagination has
become a delusion!
(Shizune)
Looks like he's
about to be eliminated
from the competition!
Lee! You Bird-brain!
Why'd you have
to say that!?
Gahhh I thought
I was helping him!
I'll deal with Neji and
Mr. Teuchi! You keep
working on the challenge!
Alright! Sorry!
(Shizune)
Team 10's Ino appears to be
in the lead by herself!
[phone ringing]
Oh? Hello! Who's
calling, please?
Sorry about this... But
it doesn't look like we're
going to be able to make it.
Excuse me?!
Choji's having some
pretty bad stomach
pains...
You're on your own.
[gasp]
This is exactly the look
people get when they find
out someone has stood them
up on Christmas!
How could this happen!?
Somebody stood me up
for Christmas!?
(Shizune)
Oh no! Ino's in shock
from being stood up on
the holiday!
(Shizune)
And there's more bad news...
Here comes Hinata!
(Shizune)
This may be it for Ino!
She's way behind now.
Alright! This means I
can get Naruto's present!
...♪...
(Shizune)
Naruto isn't coming!
That means Hinata will be
forced to spend Christmas
Eve alone!
(Lady Tsunade)
She's gonna have a silent
night, if you know what
I mean...
(Shizune)
After all the dropouts, we're
down to just Team 3's Rock Lee,
and Team 7's Naruto Uzumaki!
(Shizune)
And now, they must both
clear the final hurdle!
[gasps]
Aha! Lee and Uzumaki!
You boys have perfect
timing!
We need this paperwork
done by tomorrow...
The end of the year
is always a busy time
for us...
(Guy)
Sorry, but interns
don't get Christmas
off, good luck!
(Shizune)
What a cruel turn of events!
A literal mountain of unpaid
overtime now stands in front
of Lee and Naruto!
This is pretty awful
timing... but still!
There's no choice!
It's gotta get done!
(Naruto)
[groan] There's no end
to this paperwork!
[sigh] Christmas is
going to be over before
we get finished...
We may still be working
through New Years...
Do you wanna... end
this competition?
You sure?
Oh yes, absolutely!
A peaceful Christmas
beats a competitive one
any way you figure!
You're right!
(Shizune)
Oh my goodness! What an
incredible turn of events!
Unbelievable!
(Shizune)
A powerful friendship has
formed between these two
rivals! And here they come!
(Shizune)
Crossing the finish line
arm-in-arm!
(Lady Tsunade)
They both finish first!
(Shizune)
A tie, though, leaves
us with a little bit
of a problem...
(Shizune)
...who gets to
pick first!?
I am satisfied with
having finished the
race! You go ahead
and choose.
I wouldn't feel
right about it since
we both tied!
Mhm. Go together, and
if you want the same
present, play rock
paper scissors for it.
(Lee)
Got it!
(Naruto)
Thanks!
Mhm!
(Shizune)
Alright, gentlemen,
go ahead and pick!
-Alright!
(Naruto)
I don't know where
to start...!
(Lee)
They ALL look
interesting!
Hold on a minute...
Which one is it?
[gasps]
(Narrator)
It was at that moment that both
boys realized they had mis-
judged how the competition was.
(Narrator)
They had no idea which present
was from Sakura, so neither one
of them wa
s able to choose it.
(Narrator)
In fact, when it was over,
both Lee and Naruto got
each other's presents!
Merry Christmas..! And
Happy New Year, everybody!
Ho ho ho!
(Narrator)
Thank you, everyone, for
being such loyal viewers
this past year!
(Narrator)
Here at the Hidden Leaf Village,
the seasons have changed, and
t's time for the annual clean up
Good to see everyone!
Today, you're all going out
to clean up the year's worth
of dirt and clutter that has
built up here in the Village!
An entire year's
worth of dirt..?
Oh boy...
Over the run of this show,
you've all been responsible
for an enormous amount of
trouble...
By your behavior, you've
thrown the entire schedule
into chaos, and inconvenienced
the production staff!
It's time to wipe the
slate clean and start
over!
Oh really? And this is
your solution!?
We go to work and
sweep everything
under the rug!?
"Clean Up Is A Chance
To Wash Away The Past"
Looks like we've been
assigned to clean out
the storehouse in the
western part of the village.
Yes, but to be perfectly
honest, I would much
rather be training.
Oh quit complaining.
Do you wanna get
some New Year's
noodles after this?
Sounds like a great idea!
After that, we can go
listen to the temple
bells ring in the new year!
I'll ask Ino if
she wants to go!
Ahhh!
[excited sounds]
Let's get all of our
cleaning done quickly!
All of a sudden Lee
seems really motivated!
He overheard Naruto
and Sakura talking about
going out for soba noodles.
And he expects to
be included?
Hey! Why are you
lollygagging!?
If you keep slacking
off like this, I will
be cleaning you up, Neji.
That's not the kind of cleaning
we're supposed to be doing, and
while we're on the subject, who
are you, anyway!?
Alright, fine! But we
need to finish the job
as quickly as possible!
If we do...!
[gong]
[running breaths]
[happy giggle]
[goofy chuckle]
What are you
imagining!?
Spending New Year's
Eve with Sakura...
It's one thing to have an
ulterior motive, mister,
but you're taking it way
too far!
This is not
helping!
If we keep joking
around, I will miss
the soba noodles and
the singing as well!
We have to speed
this up... Great
Leaf Hurricane!
Good heavens!
Stop it! What
are you doing?!
And fore!
Hey! We're not
golfing!
Now what do we do?
All of those important
documents got blown away.
Do not worry. I will
go out and pick them
all up.
You mean all by
yourself?!
Hey! I will be fine!
Believe me, I can handle
this job in my sleep!
In the end, it is a lot
easier than tracking down
those seven spheres that
grant your wish!
You're really pushing
it now, mister!
We're all doing this
clean-up because you
keep pulling stunts!
Idiot..! Idiot..!
At least they
did not blow
far away!
Hinata? What
is going on?
Oh, hi, Lee.
Good morning.
I was just about to
mail a New Year's
card when a big gust
of wind came up!
There were a lot of
papers in the air.
Oh... really? That
is too bad! I need
to go now!
That card was
really important.
I don't know how I'm
going to find it!
Uh... well... if that
is true, I suppose I
could stay and help
you look for it...
Huh? Is this it?
"A very happy New Year
to you, Naruto."
"Thank you for everything
you've done for me. I
hope we grow closer."
Not 'grow closer!' You
misread what I wrote
down!
Why would I write
'closer...?'
Actually, it says
"closed stir!"
Naruto has a talent when
he makes instant ramen!
Some people just stick a
spoon in, but he uses a
'closed stir' technique.
And that way-- he
doesn't get burned!
It's something he...
came up with... and it
belongs... to him!
(Narrator)
Hinata's embarrassment
has overwhelmed her,
and she's down!
Stay with me, and
hang in there, Hinata!
I will get help!
Oh! Lady Tsunade! I
am glad you are here!
Hinata just fainted!
Is there something
wrong?
Well, actually,
there is.
I discovered I had won a
prize in the lottery.
I was on my way to claim
it when a gust of wind
blew through, and swept
the ticket away!
What a mess! It would
have been my first and
last win of the year!
I don't know where
that wind came from...
Uhh... me neither!
I hate to run off
like this, but could
you take care of
Hinata!?
I have got to find that
ticket, so I can go off
and have New Years
noodles with Sakura!
(Mr. Teuchi)
Oh! What a disaster!
Mr. Ichiraku Ramen?
What seems to be
the matter..?
It was weird... This
huge gust of wind came
along and blew over all
of my ramen deliveries.
Why are we having
hurricane-force winds
at the end of December?
I'm gonna have to go
back and make a whole
new batch of ramen...
And believe me!
I had a lot to
deliver!
A stroke of crummy
luck for me...
Lousy freak wind...
Well now! Thank you for
sharing your problem! I
will try to do something
about it!
Idiot..! Idiot..!
(Neji)
Tenten! What's
the status?
(Tenten)
What do you think?
There's a lot to do.
So much got broken.
And on top of
everything else,
where on earth
did Lee go?
And what do you
think he's been doing
this whole time?
He hasn't helped
us clean one bit!
(Mr. Teuchi)
Five orders ramen,
ready to go!
(Lee)
I will be right back!
(Mr. Teuchi)
Thanks a lot, Lee!
(Lee)
Alright, I have
returned..!
(Mr. Teuchi)
Next up, we've got a
chashu and four tanmens!
On my way!!
[sobbing] I am going
to miss my New Year's
soba dinner with Sakura!
I don't get it,
where could Lee be?
I don't know, but all
the papers got picked up.
(Naruto)
New Year's soba
noodles for us,
please!
I think that's
Naruto...
Hold your horses,
Naruto! I'm still
looking. I haven't
decided yet!
I think I'll have
the barbecued soba.
I wonder if they'd
be willing to wait
around, in case Lee
happens to show up.
I would feel pretty bad
asking everyone to wait
around here on our account.
I've got it! I know how
we can pull it off! I'm
sure this will work...
Tell me...
Do you remember
our sushi test?
(Neji)
Sushi test? You mean the
one from episode 27?
(Tenten)
It doesn't matter which
episode it was!
If we create an environment
where everyone feels bad about
eating, they wont be able to
order, and they'll hang out.
(Neji)
Sounds like a plan.
So how do we do that?
I'm not worried. We've
endured a whole year of
being in Lee's skits...
Don't you think we
can come up with
something? Heh heh...
Huh...? ARGH!
Sakura, will you
hurry up and pick
something!?
Stop pushing! I'm torn
between the curry udon
and the hot-pot udon!
You're supposed to
eat soba on New Years
remember?
(Tenten)
Excuse me...
Huh?
Could I have an order
of broth and soba?
Wait a minute, sis,
I thought we were
getting tempura soba.
I'm sorry, but it's
too expensive, we
can't afford it!
When you think about it,
we should be grateful we
get to eat soba noodles at
all on New Years Eve.
It's best if we
don't get greedy...
Alright then! I'm still
happy we can have hot soba!
We'll have to share
a bowl, but that
should work out!
That's fine!
Nice, Tenten! This'll
hit em right in the heart!
It's so sad, I
can't stop crying!
I can't believe
how good broth
and soba sounds..!
After hearing them, I
can't bring myself to
order either udon dish!
Here's what I'm thinking,
let's wait for those kids
to finish before we order...
This is working
out great!
I knew it would!
Excuse me, guys...
Here we go..!
Why are you both
doing this? Tenten?
Neji?
[gasps]
He recognized us!
Well, actually...
It's kinda funny...
[gong]
Those chores took me
all day and it is so
late!
I imagine that
Sakura, Tenten, Neji,
and the others have
probably eaten by now.
(Restaurant owner)
What's going on!? Aren't
you people done yet!?
[gasp]
It's late. And I need to
close up the restaurant!
Back off, lady...
Isn't it obvious to
you my daughter's
still eating..!
Oh really?! How many
hours dos it take to
eat a bowl of soba!?
(Woman)
We're closed! Everyone
out..!
Naruto..? Tenten..?
Uh, Neji..? Everyone!?
[groans]
[gong]
You waited for me?
That is amazing.
Considering how hungry
we were, I hope you
appreciate it!
That's all well and
good, but in the end
none of us got any soba.
Hey, don't sweat it!
He's right. We'll get some
after the first of the year.
(Lee)
Can I ask...
Huh?
This meal, does it
absolutely have to
be soba..?
Hmm?!
(Mr. Teuchi)
Oh man, all that happened?!
You should have come here
in the first place.
Let me tell you, Lee
really saved my hide
earlier!
That's why your
meal is on the house!
[cheers]
[happy eating sounds]
(Narrator)
Have a wonderful holiday,
everyone! And keep watching
in the New Year!
[midnight gong ringing]
(Neji)
Wewf! It's great to finally
be done cleaning!
(Neji)
I've gotta say, it really feels
like we've washed away the shame
and regrets of the past!
(Tenten)
Yeah! I feel ready to take
on this next year!
(Neji)
I'm with you!
And to achieve that, I'm gonna
turn things around and become
a straight man character!
(Lee)
Next time on Rock Lee:
"A New Year's Escape Clause,"
and "Naruto Under Surveillance!"
(Lee)
Looks like you are the
main character in that
one, Neji!
(Lee)
Time to celebrate! Let us
raise a glass to another year
of shame and regret!
(Neji)
Noooo!