We're in the midst of a brutal
heat wave! Just thinking about
these temperatures makes me
break into a cold sweat!
Our heroes are suffering,
along with everyone else.
They can barely eat their
popsicles!
It's so hot. It's
been so hot even
at night!
I know! We need air-
conditioning or
something!
We're a sorry group
of ninjas if we need
air-conditioning to
survive!
Neji is absolutely correct!
We should solve this problem
like real ninjas...
...with wind-
style jutsu!
[screaming]
Hey. This wind is
pretty refreshing!
Nice job there, Lee!
But why is it so wet?
Oh yuck! That
stuff is sweat!
Cut it out, Lee!
This is gross!
This isn't ninjutsu!
Really! It
doesn't even
exist!
You're getting everyone
worked up! Cut it out!
Alright, Lee!
Enough!
We're just gonna have to
beg Guy Sensei to get an
air conditioner installed!
Denied.
There are countless ways
to cool off without air-
conditioning, and we're
going to try one of them now.
That outfit gives
me a bad feeling.
Oh yes, a summer ghost
story! Tonight, we'll all
tell scary tales and in
the process, everyone's
spine will be full
of chills!
I call this little
exercise my 'I-swear-
it-really-happened'
ghost story training!
What?! You do ghost
story training?!
Interesting...
Oh! Keep it
to yourself!
Beg your pardon.
A Hot Night for a
Chilling Tale.
Alright, we're all in our
places, with bright shiny
faces. We'll start with
you, Lee. Tell us a story
so scary, it will make
our teeth chatter!
As you wish...
I have given this some
thought, and I have decided
to tell you the gory details
of something awful that
happened to me just
the other day.
This story centers around the
discovery of one particular
video tape. I hope your hearts
can handle it!
[screaming]
Zip it!
Let me ask something...
This video is it the kind
of thing where you die one
week after you view it?
No, that is kid's stuff.
The horrors I endured
were much more scary.
But as I look back on
the incident...
...I realize how lucky
I am to still be alive.
It was a dark and stormy
night. I had finally gotten
around to cleaning my room.
While going through my
closet, I came across a
very old VHS tape, way
in the back.
What the heck
is that?
As I knelt there, a
feeling of foreboding
crept into my heart.
There was no
mistaking it...
I remembered that tape!
It was one I had rented
over three years ago,
and still had not returned!
[crying]
I'm telling you, the late
fees are going to bankrupt
me!
Just thinking about
returning it terrifies
me!
That's not the kind of
scary we were looking for.
Oh. Did I misunderstand?
Let me just take a look
in here.
Material for jokes?!
That night, after putting it
off for months, I finally got
around to cleaning out the
refrigerator. Suddenly, I saw
something deep in the
rear of the veggie drawer.
It was a year-old potato!
[screaming]
Wrong again!
You really do not
believe that is scary?!
Of course not!
Are you nuts?!
I am not talking about
nuts here, my friend!
Do you have any idea
how terrifying a year-
old potato can actually
look?! Have you ever seen
one up close and personal?
It is all wriggly and squishy
and yucky, let me tell
you, it is absolutely
horrifying!
Regardless, it's not
the right kind of scary!
We need to hear about
ghosts, and monsters,
and that kind of stuff!
She's right, Lee! Just
because it's something that
might have scared you, doesn't
make it a ghost story.
You're next, Naruto.
Tell us your story.
Alright, but thinking
about it really freaks
me out.
In fact, I nearly put it
out of my memory. This
happened a few years ago,
but it seems like it took
place only yesterday.
It was late at night,
and I had to hit the
bathroom...
[groan]
Suddenly, I heard a
sad voice moaning in
pain! I was petrified!
[groaning]
It wasn't going away!
Slowly I turned, and
looked out the window.
And then I saw it! There
were tears streaming down
the carved face of the
old Third Hokage!
[screaming]
And that's my scary
story! It was pretty
freaky, don't you think?
Uhh... That was
me, Naruto!
What?
I had been up there.
[grunting]
I really had a
challenge that
night.
I was doing ten thousand
pull-ups on the Stone
Faces, and boy was I
sweaty!
It was nothing more
than your grunts and
sweat?!
You fail, Naruto. That
was not a scary ghost
story. Next up is
Konohamaru!
Alright, I'm ready! Listen
up, I've got a really scary
story for everybody!
It was the day we all
went to the opening of
that new curry restaurant!
Only three of us went in to
eat, but for some mysterious
reason, the waitress served
us four plates of food!
You mean to say there
was someone invisible
sitting next to you in
the booth?!
What was it,
a hungry ghost?!
Would you mind
letting go of me?
Oh! Sorry about
that, guys!
I guess I accidentally
put in that extra order.
It was you again?!
Sorry, but I'm afraid
that's not a ghost story
either. You're up, Sakura.
I don't really have
a story. But I want you
to look at something.
It's very interesting.
It's a picture taken of all
of us from the day we went
down to the beach.
Ooohhh!
Is that a spirit I see?
Whoa!
Sorry folks! I guess
that was just me farting!
[laughing]
You mean you actually
fart visible clouds?!
How gross! So that's
what that smell was!
I remember now!
Is everything around
here, Bushy-Brow's fault?!
So much for scary tales. This
whole thing is turning into
some kind of bad comedy act.
[sigh]
It's your turn,
Tenten. Go for it.
Uh...
Well, alright, I'll take a
shot. This didn't actually
happen to me, but Lady
Tsunade once told me a story.
If you go up to the girl's
bathroom on the third floor
of the Academy building,
you'll find there is
a row of mirrors...
At 3:33 am, if you look
into the third mirror from
the back, something strange
will happen...
You'll see a face
that's not your own!
[screaming]
You mean that's
really true?!
W-Wait a minute! Are
you saying there's a
ghost in there?
Was it you again, Lee?
Come on, tell the truth.
Oh no, even for me, that
is too much. I do not hang
around girl's bathrooms in
the wee hours of the morning.
Then what?!
Hmm...
With no other explanations,
do you think it could have
been a real spirit?
We should go find out.
It's almost 3:33 right
now.
How do you feel about
a test of courage?
Are you up for it?
What?!
Now that I've thought
about it, I think we
should go back.
It is pretty creepy
wandering around here
in the middle of the
night.
Also, apart from the creep
factor, it's hotter than
blazes up here.
You're right. And all this
running around isn't making
it any better.
[screaming]
What was that noise?
Sorry, that was just
the sound of me
sweating again.
Who has loud sweat?!
[groaning]
Okay, this is the
girl's bathroom.
First, I had better
use my Sexy Jutsu.
I'm sure that's
quite unnecessary!
Go ahead, it's the
third mirror from
the back.
Guys, do you really think
we'll see someone else
in that mirror?
There's only one way
to know. Check it out,
Naruto.
Wait! Did we vote? Why
does it have to be me?
Stop!
You have gone this far,
do not chicken out now!
The clock says it
is almost 3:33!
Stop it, Lee!
I don't wanna!
[screaming]
Well, so far, all I
see is the two of us.
Me, too. Guess it was
just another tall tale.
Lady Tsunade was sure
she saw something!
Lady Tsunade?
[screaming]
Oh!
I have it figured out!
Lady Tsunade must have
gone to the bathroom at
that very early morning
hour, and caught a glimpse
of her own face without any
makeup!
[screaming]
I hear someone
talking about me!
What about my face?
Is that Lady Tsunade?!
Oh my god,
the horror!
[screaming]
It is weird, but now I
definitely see a face other
than my own in the mirror.
All the ghost stories
turned out to be nothing
but duds.
Trust me, humans are
the scariest creatures
you'll ever meet.
Apparently, there's no
such things as ghosts,
after all.
You are the only one
who has not gone yet.
Uh, right.
In that case, it's
your turn, and you're
our last hope.
Show everyone how it's
done, and tell us a
terrifying tale that will
chill us to the bone!
Yes, of course.
This is my chance to come
through. I really need to
nail it. But I don't know
any truly scary stories.
It's just not my thing.
Where do I begin?
You can do this!
Yeah! Go for it!
My friends...
That's it! I've got a
story! I remember now!
The question is, should I
go ahead and tell them?
There'd be no taking it back
afterwards, that's for sure.
I can do this! This is
no time to waver! I need
to be strong!
This is a story I was told
years ago when I was a
child, about a wolf-man.
Uh... Did you say
wolf-man?
[nervous groans]
Once, on a night with
a full moon...
...a man whose wild, unkempt
hair blew in the wind, took
a comb from his pocket and
howled...
[nervous groans]
I'm shedding!
Agh...
So awful.
Even though it's a sweltering
night, everyone in the room
is frozen in fear. But what
happens next?
Please! Don't
punish me!!
Summer is the season for
adventures! And with each
season and each adventure,
young boys climb the steps
toward manhood!
My dream is simple. I want
to become the youngest
Hokage in history!
The Hokage's Tears
Aren't for Decoration!
Time for a pop quiz,
everyone! In the first
half of the episode, it
seemed Lee was behind all
the scary happenings in
everyone's ghost stories.
But actually, one phenomenon
was real! Did you notice
which one?
The answer is right in
front of you! But for those
of you who missed it, we'll
take another look. Lee, as
you may remember, was
doing pull-ups on the
First Hokage's eye as
part of his training.
Naruto then said
the following...
There were tears streaming
down the carved face of the
old Third Hokage!
Wait a minute! You're
telling us the Stone
Face was actually crying?!
I remember 'The Tears of
the Great Stone Faces' was
one of the 'Seven Mysteries
of the Leaf' we learned
about when we were
back at the Academy.
Perhaps this was a
real paranormal event,
after all.
[nervous groans]
[crying]
It's time we stopped
the ghost stories, okay?
I'll solve this mystery,
once and for all!
The narrator even said
that the summer is the
season for adventure.
Konohamaru, you
are not scared?
Well of course not! He may
have died, but the Third
Hokage's still my grandpa!
I could get to see him
again, and if he's upset
for some reason, I'd want
to help!
I hadn't thought about
it, but it's possible
his ghost is trying to
tell us something.
Seriously, can we cool
it with the ghost talk,
guys!
Actually...
[screaming]
Tsu-! Tsu-!
Lady Tsunade?
I saw it myself,
last night.
I got up to go to
the bathroom again...
And then...
Huh?! What?!
The eyes were flashing!
[screaming]
[scared cries]
[scream]
What is wrong, Naruto?
The Third Hokage's
eye! I saw it move!
You sure about that?
I don't see
anything strange.
You are becoming a real
scaredy-cat, Naruto.
Ah! I'm telling you I
saw it move! You've gotta
believe me!
Yes, the eye definitely
moved, as I'm sure you
noticed. But I'm here to
tell you, it was not any
kind of paranormal event!
It was all because of this
man. Say, what are you doing
here, anyway?
What does it look like?
I'm setting up a base,
here on the edge of the
Leaf Village!
From here, I can observe Rock
Lee and his friends, and then
attack them the second they
let their guard down!
[laughing]
I feel much better!
Excuse me, do I have this
right? Is it possible the
Hokage's tears are nothing
but toilet water?!
Oh my goodness!
Look, he's crying!
I told you that's
what was going on!
Ah! What in the
world is this?!
Hey, come back here!
Are you going where
I think you're going?!
No one's going
anywhere without
me!
Good luck, everyone.
What is it, Lee?!
Is the Third Hokage
watching shows on
this TV?
Finally saw Muben's
Elevation of the Boss.
That's it, boy! Keep
wagging that tail for me!
You really lost it, Lee!
Quit joking around!
Sorry, guys.
Anyway, we should check
out the stone faces.
So far, I don't see
anything unusual.
[screaming]
What is it?!
Is that snot
dripping on you?
Sorry about that. I
seem to be sweating
quite a lot.
What, again?!
Really, again?!
You're doing
that again?!
I do apologize, but on the
plus side, I found something
really amazing in here!
Come and look!
What in the world?
Is this a natural cave?
Hey, Naruto...
What's up, Bushy-
[screaming]
Enough! Both
of you!
Oh, darn it! My front-
line base was just days
from being finished!
You're telling me
this isn't done yet?
Of course not!
Open your eyes and take a
look around. Tell me what
you see! I want to have a
trendy urban space, not
some crude cave!
A 37th-floor penthouse, a
beautiful night sky. High-
end furniture and high-
end wine. And of course,
a robe made entirely
of real silk!
Sounds great, but isn't
it a little fancy for a
hideout?
There's only one way to
protect this space. I'll
just have to scare them
off!
Let's see how
they like this!
[whimpering]
Yam paste?
Yam paste hit you. So
you know what is coming
next, right?
I haven't got a clue.
You have to undergo
a boiling bath!
What in the world are you
talking about?!
[yelling]
The boiling bath is the
traditional punishment!
Wait a minute! How in the
world did this even get
in here!
I've got this.
Byakugan!
Hmm...
Lavender Bath Bombs!
You're adding
bath salts?!
[screaming]
What is this place,
a haunted house?
Sure seems like it.
Let's keep going.
No positive results, I'm
afraid. Only one of them
was even remotely scared.
Those accursed brats! I
guess now I'll be forced
to use my secret weapon!
Let's see how they
deal with this!
[gasp]
Where in the heck
did this tape come
from?
My lord, is that one of
those tapes you have a
week to return?
Yes it is.
If you don't get it back
to the store at the end of
that one week, it will start
to accure late fees!
I rented it over
three years ago and
completely forgot
about it!
[screaming]
Excuse me, but there's no
point in you being scared!
Is what's on the tape going
to frighten these kids?!
Umm, we already used
this bit earlier...
I wonder what
could be on it.
Neji, if you please.
Byakugan!
Good god! It's the
'Make-Out Tactics'
movie!
The Byakugan can even
see what's on the tape?!
I can't believe you rented
that one. I've been trying
to see it for years, but
every time I go to the video
store, they tell me their
only copy is still checked
out!
So it's been all because
of you, damn it!
Wow...
I think you've seen
enough of this!
It was just
getting good!
Hey! We can watch
it at my house!
It's not going
to your house!
This sure doesn't feel
like much of a summer
adventure.
No peeking, Neji!
[gasp]
Well, I'm down to my last
option! No more time for
playing around!
[gasps]
Darn it!
What's going on?!
Are you okay in
there?! Talk to me!
Konohamaru! Go get
Guy Sensei and the
other teachers!
Alright! Just hang
tight, I'll be back
soon!
I think not.
You're the one who's
behind this, aren't you?!
[laughing]
And the way things are
going, my secret base may
not even need renovating!
You are all finished!
No! Lemme go!
You've got them now,
Lord Orochimaru!
And they're all going
to pay the price!
What's that?!
I'm not sure...
Fireballs?
Don't look at me! I'm
not the one who's doing
this!
What is going on here?!
Grandpa?!
[gasps]
Look out below!
Here we come!
I don't know how he was
able to do it, but
grandpa saved me...
[gasp]
And another Orochimaru
plan goes up in smoke!
Considering how things
turned out, maybe spirits
do exist!
Mmhmm!
Keep watching over me,
grandpa, and I'll be Hokage
one day, and make you proud!
We have been assigned student
teaching positions! I cannot
wait to teach the students about
ninjutsu! It will be great!
I'm sure we'll be fine,
but I am a little concerned.
Do not worry! It is simple.
We will simply teach the kids
everything we have learned
ourselves!
I feel better now.
On the next episode:
'Always Do Your Homework at
the Last Minute!' and 'Class-
Three Lee! We Are a Team Guy!'
I gotta tell you, someone
who says, always do your
homework at the last minute
makes me a little uncomfortable.