We're still in the dog
days of summer, so how does
a nice, refreshing fireworks
show sound?
So a fireworks show?
That's right, it's
going to be part of the
festival. Now here's
where you come in...
What we'd like is for
each team to create their
own unique fireworks
display using chakra
and fire-style jutsu!
Oooh!
We're making it a
contest and every team
will participate.
The most spectacular
display will win.
Lee, I'll be honest,
your inability to use
ninjutsu will put you at
a huge disadvantage.
But it's just another trial
to overcome. So go and
win this thing!
Yes, sir!
Boom! The Shinobi
Fireworks Show.
Holy cow!
Everyone's really pushing
themselves. It's gonna be
tough to beat all of them,
that's for sure.
So what is our best shot
at winning?
We need to come up with
something that will leave
everyone speechless,
otherwise we have no
chance of winning.
Right, something that
will leave them
speechless.
How about this?
You're joking--A
sparkler?
Striking a pose and
letting the sparks fly
would definitely do the
trick, I think.
Oh, it'll leave them
speechless all right.
Out of boredom.
All right.
How about this--what if I
strap a bunch of fireworks
to my body and become a
living spinner?
That will shock
them!
The only one guaranteed
to be shocked is you, you
bonehead!
Fine!
I will become a human
rocket and launch myself
into the sky--that will
blow them all away!
Lee! You're going to
blow everyone, including
yourself, UP!!
Boom!
Boy... I guess this is
going to be tougher than
I thought.
Lee!
Huh?
Wow, Sakura, you look
beautiful in your yukata!
Haha, why thank you!
S-so, Sakura, w-what kind
of fireworks do you like?
Um, Lee...
The kind that really
knocks your socks off,
right?
What in the blue blazes
are we wearing?!
Or maybe the really
extravagant variety?!
How'd I get dragged
into all of this?!
Oops, I lit it.
Put it out, you idiot!
Would if I could!
Hey! Kakashi Sensei!
It's okay having a little
fun, but remember, fire
isn't a toy.
And that goes for you
folks watching, too!
Use your fireworks
responsibly!
Oink, oink.
Are you going to enter
the contest, too, Sensei?
Not a chance. I'm just
here in case of any fire
emergencies. Just shout
if you need me.
I want to come up with a
display that will really
wow the audience, but I
can't seem to figure
anything out.
Fancier fireworks are
definitely fun, but I
think I like the simpler
ones best.
Huh?
All right, let's all do
our best you guys!
So something simpler,
huh? That settles it!
Okay! We will do something
simple. Like launching a
human firework into deep
space!
You know what
simple means, right?
What the hell's going
on, you guys?
Ehh--
[laughing and cheering]
I love fireworks!
All right!
This is it, guys and
gals! The time has
finally come!
For the Leaf Village
Fireworks Show!
Leading off is Team
Seven!
Let's launch this bad boy
already!
[grunting]
He threw it!
Whoa! Team Seven used a
wind-style jutsu to make
a giant windmill
firework!
Color commentator Lady
Tsunade, what's your
take?
It looks like an enormous
roulette wheel.
There you have it,
folks!
Man! That's pretty
awesome!
Great job, Naruto!
Big deal. I could do
that!
Leaf Whirlwind!
Lee! You don't need to
spin yourself!!
[squealing]
Suh-Sakura!!
Oh no! It looks like
Naruto's arsenal went off
right where it counts!
So tell us, what did you
think of the windmill
display, m'lady?
Looked just like a slot
machine jackpot.
And there you have it.
They're only halfway through
their entire set, but it's
gonna be hard to outdo
Naruto's fireworks display.
I know, Tenten.
Neji!
Forget it, Lee!
Next up, Team Eight!
Bankrolled by the Hyuga
clan's ample wealth, Team
Eight has constructed a
massive and extravagant
array of fireworks!
Well, care to weigh in,
Lady Tsunade?
I feel like I'm
watching someone else
hit the jackpot.
There you have it.
[gasping in awe]
Whoaaa, that is awesome,
Hinata!
N-Naruto's watching,
gotta do my best!
We can't compete with
fireworks this fancy!
What do we do, Lee?
Do not worry, if you act
now, I will throw in an
extra firework for free!
Uch! This isn't the
shopping network!
So you two are really
still at it, huh?
[grunting]
Huh?
Oh my gosh, Hinata!
[lightly groaning]
N-N-N-N...
Not again!
Lady Hinata!
Ohh, it looks like the
fire burning in
Hinata's heart set off
the rest of the fireworks
early! Care to give a
comment, Lady Tsunade?!
Trust me, I feel for her.
You gotta have that fire in
your heart before every roll
of the dice.
And there you have it.
If we really wanna beat
them, we're gonna have
to come up with something
fancier than a human
sparkler. But we just
don't have that kind of
money to spend.
It is cool, Tenten.
Huh?
We have still got plenty of
time. Let us do a fundraiser.
Wait a minute, are you
selling yakisoba?
Oh no, we have got more
than that.
Okonomiyaki, takoyaki,
and chocolate bananas!
What kind of crazy menu
is that?!
Besides---This is
supposed to be serious
contest, no one's gonna
stop to eat, you weirdos!
Oh look, a customer.
[gobbling]
Will you stop eating!?
All right! Team Ten
is on deck!
Ah man what a drag.
Ooh!
Shikamaru's expert Shadow
Pull gives us a masterful
display of timed fireworks
this evening.
Don't you think, Lady
Tsunade?
A masterful display of
cheating is more like it.
Can we please get away
from the gambling
analogies for five
seconds?!
Whoa.
Shikamaru's team did
pretty well, too!
Okay, that does it!
I will go myself
if I have to.
It's time for the
finale, Choji.
[gobbling]
What the heck are you
eating?!
Takoyaki.
Seriously, dude, do you
really have to do that
right now? What is the
matter with you?
Hey when I'm hungry, I
eat.
[gasping]
[screaming]
Uh oh!
It appears Choji has
accidentally eaten a ball
of fireworks!
Huh??
Aaagh! Don't come over
here!
Ugh, what else could go
wrong tonight?
I've been waiting for
this chance!
Huh?!
That's-!!
Orochimaru!
I'll use all the
confusion to light my
giant black snake!
Whaaaaat?!
Ugh, darnit! I can barely
move a muscle in this
outfit!
Hey, Naruto!
He's down for the count!
Maybe Guy Sensei
can help!
It's no good, the heat
from the takoyaki KO-ed
him!
Well I suppose it's all
up to me, then.
Ulgh, it's you.
The Leaf's airhead
funny man.
Uh! An airhead?!
I'm not the airhead
funnyman!
Where do you think
you're going?!
Fine, I'll handle
you myself.
Ah... The resident
straightman, eh?
Resident straightman..?!
It's not like I enjoy it,
okay?! I don't know what
I'm doing with my life!
Not you, too!
Welp, that is it for
Neji and Tenten.
Alright, buckle in,
everyone.
That is it!
I need to wake Kakashi
Sensei!
Sakura!
'Kay, you're lit.
Hm?
Kakashiiii Senseiiiii!
What?!
Kakashi Sensei, we will
need a water jutsu
please...
O-Okay...
[snarling]
Oh noooooo!
And just like that, the
fireworks show came to an
end, thanks to Orochimaru's
machinations.
It's too bad they had to
cancel the show, huh?
Yes.
It was tough waking up
Kakashi Sensei. I ended
up using the only halfway
decent fireworks I had.
I wish I could've seen
what you came up with.
Oh, actually, I have some
left.
Just some boring old
sparklers. You wanna
light them up with me?!
[gasping]
You know, when all is
said and done, I think I
like simpler stuff like
this the best.
Uh, Sakura?
Huh?! What the heck?!
Do not worry, if you act
now, I will throw in an
extra firework for free!
An extra firework...
And so, Lee's feelings,
and Lee himself, were
scattered across the
heavens.
Sakura!
Lee?
And remember everyone!
Use fireworks
responsibly!
The season of love. Maybe
it's this season, when
the sun shines so
bright...
Impressive as always!
Looks like I will have
to use my special move
that only works in the
summer!
Huh? You have a move that
utilizes the summer??
Haaaaaaa!
Behold, the Summer Wrap!
My summertime specialty!
Lee! Summer wraps
are dresses!
This is a kid's show,
you're going over the
audience's head!
Would you please back me
up over here, Tenten.
Huh?
[sighing]
Bang! Tenten's
Acting Weird!
[sighing]
Something is
wrong.
Tenten is just not her
usual energetic self
lately, is she? You think
something happened maybe?
I'm really starting to
worry... we need to snap
her out of this funk
she's in somehow.
We don't want to lose
our straight man.
Our straight man...
That is it! I have got
the perfect way of
getting Tenten back to
her normal self!
Hm?
[sighing]
Oh man, it is so hot!
Ugh, on days like this...
... you really
crave something
cold!
Hey, leave it to me!
It's been five years
since we started
dating...
We used to go to all
kinds of places, but
lately...
... it's just been
whatever restaurant
we're closest to.
Pass the sauce.
Um...
I was thinking.. Maybe we
should um... ya know,
break up.
Sure. If that is
really what you want,
I am cool with it.
I'm... kidding.
Give it a rest.
A shocking amount of
relationships... just
grow cold.
Nice, Lee! Tenten's the
number one straight man
on our show. Any second,
she'll-
That's the wrong kind of
cold, you blockheads!!
She'll be back
to normal.
Come on, Tenten! You can
do it! Let us have it!
[sighing]
Something is definitely
wrong!
We have seriously got
to do something, Neji!
Yes, but the question
right now is what?
If it's this grave,
it'll be hard to ask
her about it.
Still, we will just
have to give it a shot.
Yum!
Darling, you make the
best veggies in the whole
world!
Oh, you. Such a kidder.
[sighing]
So tell me, sweet pea,
how is, uh, school going?
You finally starting
to make some friends
over there?
If there's anything on
your mind, you can always
talk to your father.
Trust me, kiddo, your
Daddy may not look like
much, but everyone at
work comes to me with
their troubles, believe
you me!
Oh my, isn't that nice,
Tenko?
[sighing]
Tenko, wait a minute!
I am your father,
I--
It is hopeless! There
is nothing we can do!
We just keep digging
ourselves deeper!
[sighing]
Hm? Hey, Bushy-Brows!
Neji! Why the long faces?
Oh, Naruto!
Ahhh!
Tenten's feeling down,
huh?
That doesn't sound
good... how long's she
been acting this way?
I would say...
It started sometime
around the fireworks
show, I think.
Why would that get her
down? Oh, hey! I've got
it!
She probably wants to set
off more fireworks!
You really think that is
what it is?
Now that you mention
it...
I'm surprised I didn't
see that, I mean it's
always a bit sad when
those shows are over.
Right then, if we know
the problem, let us
fix it!
Tenten!
Hm?
Since the fireworks show
got shut down halfway
through, Neji and I were
thinking we could put on
a little light show of
our own tonight!
You'll join us, won't
you? We bought a whole
variety!
I've got Sparklers,
spinners...
Everything from the big
blasts to black snakes!
[gasping]
And it would not be a
party without rockets!
[grunting]
Not this again!
[panicking]
[screaming]
Why meeeeee!
[sighing]
Hmmm...
So it wasn't the
fireworks, huh?
Afraid not.
Maybe... there's some
important clue we're
missing.
Hmmmm...
Whatcha doing?
Choji, hey! Do you recall
anything important
we have forgotten about
the fireworks show?!
Something important...
AGGHH!!!
We forgot to eat a
chocolate-covered banana!
Could that be it?
Chocolate-covered
banana?
Yes, that must be it.
Obviously Tenten did not
partake in the culinary
delight!
It's elementary really,
women love treats! I
don't know a woman
without a sweet tooth!
There is no time to
lose! Let us go!
Feast your eyes on this,
Tenten, we made a chocolate
fountain for you!
And we've got plenty of
goodies for dipping,
too! Some berries,
sponge cake-
Not to mention some
rice and spaghetti for
higher-quality carbs
thrown in to boot!
Mmm...
Hm?
Anyway, let us eat until
we are covered head to toe
in chocolate!
[gagging]
[sighing]
I give up.
Same here... I'm all out
of ideas.
Yeah, I guess I got
nothing either, you guys.
Hey, why don't you
ask Shikamaru? He'll
probably know.
Oh yeah, Shikamaru.
We should have started
with him... Shikamaru's
IQ is over 200, he'll
know what to do!
Huh?
Oh man, you guys are
dumber than a pile of
rocks. She turned down
chocolate, she just
sighed at fireworks, and
you really still don't
know?
There's only one thing on
earth that'll drop a
woman into that kind
of funk.
Well, do not just stand
there, tell us!
Love, my friend. Love.
Whaaat?!
L-L-L-Love?! Tenten
is--uhhh!
He's right, that
depressed attitude is
just what you'd expect of
someone tortured by love!
She drop any hints
recently?
She bump into anyone
lately? An old flame?
[gasping]
Of course, it all makes
sense now! Now I understand!
Tenten has been--
Neji, follow me! There
is no time to waste! Tenten
needs our help, ASAP!
What're you talking
about, Lee?!
Hey!
Hm?
What's with all the
long faces, you guys?
Huh?
Lady Tsunade...
What's wrong? You look
somewhat troubled.
Yeah... a
little.
Well moping won't help,
ya wanna talk about it?
Ya might feel better if
ya get it off your chest.
Hm.
Lady Tsunade...
it's just that--
What?!
He called you the
"resident straightman"?!
Yeah. During the
fireworks show...
Ugh. The resident
straightman, eh?
The resident
straightman?
It's not like I enjoy it,
okay?! Oh, I don't know
what I'm doing with my life.
Uh--
[crying]
Ever since...
Hey, look!
It's the stooge!
Let us have it!
Aaaahhh!
Maybe I only do
punchlines, and sarcastic
remarks, but everyone's
constantly setting me up!
It's not like it's
my "thing" or anything.
And honestly? It's
gotten to the point
where
I'm really starting
to question what I'm
doing with my life.
Well if you want my advice,
I'd say don't sweat it 'cause
you're fine the way you are.
Huh?
Plus, Lee and Neji are
worried sick about you.
They don't know what to
do with themselves.
Huh?
Wait, really?
Chin up now, Tenten, your
reactions are what keep
everyone on their toes.
Are you with me here?
Uh--
Yes! And thank
you so much!
Well, well, well, speak
of the devil.
Huh?
Lee, Neji...
I'm really sorry I had
you guys so worried about
me.
Not at all, we should
be apologizing.
We finally realized what
was wrong.
You've clearly been
weighed down by a
romantic quandary.
Huh?!
And really... in
hindsight, the signs
you were showing were
obvious.
Wait... What??!
And given who he is, I
don't blame you in the
least for being upset.
After all, this is a
forbidden of love we are
dealing with here.
But we steeled ourselves
and headed out to talk to
him about it!
Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa--
hold on a second-who
exactly did you go and
see?!?
Who else? Orochimaru,
of course!
Tenten is in
love with you!
Please, at least meet
with her!
What the what?!?!?
You've gotta be
kidding me! You can
just forget it!
[straining]
Put him out of your mind,
there are plenty of fish
in the sea.
Yeah, so cheer up, okay,
Tenten?
[anger building]
What?! What?!
Are both of your heads
broken or something?!?!?!
Ah!
I mean how stupid
are you two?!
How can you say that?!
The only one's who
are gonna have heart
problems are you!
[groaning]
Idiot! Idiot!
Tenten, the truth is,
without you... we really
don't have a show.
I am so glad you're not
upset anymore, Tenten!
Now look at the line up
for next time! Summer means
Seashell Styles and
Watermelon Wars!
What does Seashell Styles
even mean? It doesn't
make any sense, even for
a summer show!
Yeah, that is
a weird one, huh?
I have previewed it, too.
None of the girls in the
show have what I would
call "watermelons".
Shut up! That's not what
the title means!
Ow, Tenten!! Your
reactions are even more
intense now than ever!