Orochimaru has slammed the
Hidden Leaf Village with a
blizzard, with temperatures
at 140 degrees below zero!
(Orochimaru)
The Hidden Leaf Village
has been obliterated!
Trapped by Orochimaru's fearsome
attack, our hero, Rock Lee, has
been shackled to a stone, and
is about to meet his end!
So.. are you ready?
I'm going to take my
time torturing you!
What exactly are you
going to do to me?!
For starters...
[fearful yell]
[chuckles]
What do you
think of this?!
[panicked yell]
There! You've been marked
for life, so start dancing,
clown!
[chuckles]
Orochimaru finally achieved
his life goal. He conquered
the Leaf Village and lived
happily ever after.
An Endless Nightmare!
[chuckles/snoring]
Is something wrong,
Lord Orochimaru?!
Nom nom, wonderful...
Huh? Kabuto?
Huh?! What? You've got
to be kidding me! You mean
it was nothing but a dream?!
It appeared that you
were talking in your
sleep, m'lord.
Curse your bones, Kabuto!
You've ruined a wonderful
fantasy!
You're not supposed
to wake someone
when they're having
a good dream!
I'll let it slide.
The truth is, that dream has
given me an incredible idea!
Just you wait...
Rock Lee!
[heavy breathing]
[sneeze]
It's freezing
out here!
He's right, the
temperature has
really dropped.
The forecast predicted
record lows today.
With these conditions,
we should probably head
to the village.
No way! In this situation,
we should train ten-- No,
wait, I take that back..
We should be training
a hundred times harder!
We have to conquer
these conditions!
You think you're tough?
Let's see how long you
can endure this blizzard!
[chuckles]
[groans]
It's getting worse!
Let's take shelter
in that cave!
[heavy breathing]
(Sakura)
Doesn't look like
it's gonna let up.
I may freeze
to death!
Let me handle
this situation!
I will start my workout
with ten thousand squats,
and after that, I am going
to speed up!
Lee's hot-bloodedness
comes in handy in times
like these!
Huh? Ew!
Ew! It's so cold,
his sweat is freezing
before it hits the ground!
[grossed groan]
Id...iot...
[grunt]
I have to tell you, doing ten
thousand of these squats...
...and over thirty-thousand
Shimura-style forms has
completely wiped me out.
It has made me
really sleepy...
No, Lee!
If you fall asleep,
you'll die!
I hear you. The only way to
save myself is to count sheep.
...A sheep doing
fence hurdles!
One.. two..
and three.
That is not how
you count sheep!
Now I'm getting
kinda sleepy, too.
[yawn]
No, Sakura!
I have an idea. Why don't we
tell each other funny stories,
to keep our minds off the cold?
Funny stories,
you say?
Fine. No problem,
I have lots of them!
Stop me if you've
heard this before!
[gasp]
Hey, did I tell you
what happened?
I was in the corner store,
doing a little shopping,
When a bear walked in and
bought all the toilet paper!
That was no bear, Charlie!
That happened to be my wife!
We're all gonna
freeze to death.
It's getting
a lot colder.
We only have
one option left.
It is the last resort for
stranded mountain climbers!
We have to do
naked snuggling!
We will use our natural
body heat to keep warm!
Who is it you're
planning to
snuggle with?!
Come, Sakura!
Leap into my
bosom!
Yeah, like that's
gonna happen! You
need a reality
check, Bushy-Brows!
(Sakura)
I'm here, Lee!
Huh?
And I'm ready!
Goal!
Hey, that's no goal line!
What is all this madness?!
I had no idea you
were so warm, Lee.
Sakura, the very thought
of you makes me even
hotter than normal.
[small gasp]
You know, Lee..
I've always had
such loving
feelings for you.
Sakura, if we get out
of this situation alive,
we should go get married.
Yes. That
sounds perfect.
I can't believe what I'm
hearing! It's impossible!
Sakura, are you aware
that you just agreed
to marry Bushy-Brows?!
This isn't a genjutsu,
but honestly, something
tells me it's very wrong.
You're wrong,
everything's fine!
It just so happens
that I'm terribly
in love with Lee!
It suddenly occurs
to me that this all
might be Lee's dream.
You may be right.
I can't see this
happening in real life.
So, are you saying that I fell
asleep in real life, and this
is nothing more than some kind
of hallucination?!
And if that's truly the case,
you could easily freeze to
death in this blizzard!
AGH! Then someone
wake me up, for
heaven's sake!
I'm on it!
Eight Trigrams,
Sixty-Four Palms!
[pained groan]
Ouch!
[gasp]
Are you all
right, Lee?
I guess so. I must have
been dreaming. But you
know, that was a close one.
The blizzard's not letting
up out there and it seems
like we're all reaching our
limit.
I know I'm getting
pretty hungry.
[gasp]
That smell!
Are you kidding?!
It can't be!
Naruto, where do
you think you're
going?
After him!
[small gasp]
It is!
Have a seat!
Old man! One deluxe miso
ramen, with buttered corn
and extra pork!
It's ready
to go!
Great! It smells
wonderful!
A bowl of this will hit
the spot! It should warm
me right up!
(Tenten)
Hold on!
Huh?
This isn't a genjutsu,
but something's very
wrong!
Like, what in the world
is a ramen stand doing
in the middle of a cave?!
It suddenly occurs to me
that this all might be
Naruto's dream.
You're right. I can't
see this happening in
real life.
Whaaat?! Are you saying
that I fell asleep in real
life and this is nothing
but a hallucination?!
If that is true, that is bad!
You could very easily freeze
to death in this blizzard!
[screams]
Then someone wake
me up, for heaven's
sake!
I'm on it!
Eight Trigrams,
Sixty-Four Palms!
[pained groans]
Ow! That hurt!
Are you all
right Naruto?
I guess I am. I must have
been dreaming. That was a
close one, ya know.
The blizzard is not letting
up out there. Before long,
we will have to do something.
Huh? Where's
that sound
coming from?
Uh! Neji!
Wait, where are
you going?!
What in the world?!
Hey! She just won a new rice
cooker! The grand prize is a
Hawaiian vacation! Come and
try your luck!
We're saved!
Not unless we have
a raffle ticket!
Well! We're in
luck, I have one!
I got it with my deluxe
miso ramen, with buttered
corn and extra pork!
[grunt]
Byakugan!
That's it!
Come ooonnnn!
Congratulations!
You win the grand prize,
the Hawaiian vacation!
[cheers]
Yes! It's like summer in
Hawaii! We're all gonna make
it out of here in one piece!
Thank you
very much.
Wait! This is
wrong, too!
It makes less sense
than Naruto's fantasy!
Yeah! It suddenly occurs
to me that this all might
be Neji's dream.
Naruto?
Don't worry,
I'm on it.
Hm?
Rasengan!
Wait a--!
[pained groans]
I guess I must have
really been dreaming.
(Naruto)
Dreaming or not,
I gotta tell you,
this is a great pool!
Huh?
What?!
The fact is, the blizzard's
not letting up out there.
And the best part of
the whole thing is,
I get to talk to you,
Sakura!
Why is everyone
a capybara now?
Do not worry yourself.
Even though capybaras
all look the same, you
are still clearly a female!
That doesn't matter!
The question is, why are
you all wearing costumes
in a hot spring?!
By the way, what do
we have on underneath?
Just a suggestion.
Why not take a look
and find out?
Maybe I will!
Byakugan!
What?!
You're alpacas?
[chuckles]
Sakura is super-cute,
no matter what!
This whole thing
is madness!
Here I come!
Ready?!
Lesser...
Huh?
..Punch!
[pained yell]
Attacked by a
lesser panda?!
It's Guy Sensei!
It's time to wake
up, you fools!
This isn't working!
Y'all keep waking
up in one another's
dreams!
You need to wake up
for real, and soon
or you're going to
be dead!
So, are you telling
us that this is just
another dream?
[gasp]
Hey! What in
the world?
So cold!
Enough, already!
Whose dream is
this?
We have to wake
up before we turn
into popsicles!
Don't look at me!
This isn't my dream!
It is not
me, either!
And just for the record,
I have nothing to do with
it. It's not my dream!
If it is not ours
or the narrator's...
..then whose?!
Who is causing all
of this to happen,
and why-y-y?!
So far, so good.
Now fall into eternal
slumber Rock Lee.
Now I see who
was responsible.
What is Orochimaru doing
out here, sleeping in the
middle of a blizzard?
Well.. snakes do
hibernate, don't
they?
Hold on a second. Something
just occurred to me. Is it
possible that you, the viewers,
are dreaming all of this?
And that begs the next question:
Is anyone awake out there?
To everyone watching out there,
let me ask you a question.
Do you know what you want
to be when you grow up?
Cleaning The Great Stone Faces!
I mean, what could be more fun?!
And then...Huh?
[gasp]
Excuse me!
Who are you,
mister?
Hi I happen to be
the future Rock Lee!
[fearful scream]
A Robot From the Future!
I have to tell you the truth.
I never would have guessed
that about the First Hokage's
nostril.
It is a time tunnel that
leads thirty years into
the future?
Exactly right! And also
after all this time, I
am still a ninja who is
unable to use ninjutsu.
On top of that,
I never got it
together and
married Sakura.
Hey! Take it easy.
Get ahold of yourself!
Tell me something.
Are you sure you
are my future self?
Oh, there is no mistake!
I only ended up as this
pathetic, middle-aged
man because of you!
The fact of the matter is, if
you had been able to get your
act together back in the day,
I would not be such a loser!
Hindsight is
twenty-twenty.
Yes, and that, my boy is
why you are going to start
working hard, right now!
Huh?
Who is that?
Greetings, everyone!
I am Kabuemon, a robot
from the future!
Kabuemon?
Yes. And if you ever find
yourself in a tight spot,
you do not have to worry.
He will step up and
save you with his
future ninjutsu!
Farewell, my boy!
Wha..?
Huh?
For now, you will have
to live in my closet,
Kabuemon.
Thank you, Lee.
I have to say, my future self
certainly set me straight.
I will be careful not to end up
as such a pathetic old man.
[laughing]
I knew there was something
wrong, deep in my gut!
The plan is very simple.
Lee takes in the mysterious,
helpful robot.
They make friends and
then, the moment his
guard is down we strike!
Why am I the one that
has to do this? Normally,
Lord Orochimaru is the
man in the suit.
Oh! Kabuemon,
anything wrong?
No, no, everything's fine!
I was just thinking, if
there's anything I can help
you with, just let me know.
Remember, I'm
your best friend!
Then again, this is the first
time Lord Orochimaru has given
me such an important role.
I can't screw this up!
Idiot...Idiot.
Hello there.
I'm Kabuemon!
I'm a robot from the future.
For those of you who don't know
me, my favorite food is grilled
tuna heads!
Wow! It can talk!
So it's independent?
It moves on its own?
Yeah, absolutely!
And you're saying it
came from the future?
Tell us what our future
selves are like!
Uhh, well...
No! Please don't say
anything! I don't want
to know what my future
will be like!
I agree.
To be fair, though..
It's not that hard to
predict how Bushy-Brow's
going to turn out.
He's gonna be a pathetic,
middle-aged old man.
I plan to train hard and change
the future! And you, Kabuemon,
are gonna help me do that!
Kabue-mon!
Nine-thousand
nine-hundred
ninety..
Nine-thousand
nine-hundred
ninety-one..
Nine-thousand
nine-hundred
ninety-two..
I don't understand why a robot
has to do push-ups! But I
can't arouse any suspicions.
The success of this mission
requires that I be a helpful,
cheerful friend at all times,
no matter what the situation!
Are you sure you can
handle this? Your form
is really terrible!
Oh believe me, it's nothing!
I just suddenly had a craving
for grilled tuna heads!
[laughing]
You really are a
big eater, Kabuemon!
When we are done with the
training, I will treat you
to you much as you like!
Next, we practice
the Rasengan!
Whaa?
To do it, just spin
your body like me!
[spinning]
I have to do
this, too?
Come on,
Kabuemon!
Okay, here goes!
[spinning]
That is the spirit!
I'm gonna die!
Kabuemon!
(Naruto)
Nothing's better than
a bowl of post-training
ramen!
They only serve ramen here,
so we will get you those tuna
heads when we finish our
training later this afternoon.
Seriously, he's
still not done?!
Um, are you sure
he can handle it?
If you push him too hard,
he could very easily break
down.
Are you absolutely certain
he's a robot from the future?
I have to say, he doesn't look
all that futuristic to me.
How would we know?
I can tell you that,
for a robot, he reacts
like a human.
He almost collapsed
after the training
session this morning!
At the very least,
he is realistic!
He said something earlier about
mysterious future ninjutsu.
I wonder what he's able to do?
I bet there is all kinds of
incredible ninjutsu in the
future! Stuff we cannot even
imagine today. Am I right?
This is bad. I didn't have
time to come up with a
vision of how things will
eventually operate.
I need to think of
something futuristic..
Really futuristic.
Do you have
some examples,
Kabuemon?
Well, there are all kinds
of future ninjutsu!
Just an example, instead of
the Transformation Jutsu,
we use the Plastic Surgery
Jutsu!
Cloning techniques have
advanced to the stage of
genetic cloning.
The Sharingan now has video
recording capabilities, but
it has a limit. It only works
ten times.
Plastic surgery and genetic
cloning sound much more
complex than today's jutsu.
Interesting, and the
Sharingan only works
ten times?
I gotta say, the future actually
sounds kinda lame.
Not really! In fact,
there's plenty more...
...like Internet-style!
(Rock Lee)
Internet-style?!
Before, there was wind-style,
fire-style, water-style, and
earth-style.
Now, we've added
the newest element,
Internet-style!
You can communicate with
friends, associates, and
family, across great
distances!
[slurping]
That's surprisingly
boring.
Well, uh...
He's in trouble!
I'm gonna need
to bail him out!
Well, you see...
Huh?
So you want to know
about future ninjutsu?
Whew!
It is future me!
That's what you're
gonna look like in
thirty years, Lee?!
[chuckles]
What did I tell you?
You do look like a loser!
Where did you come
from, exactly?
You may not know this,
but there is a time-tunnel
in the back of this ramen shop.
I'm here to save
you, Kabuto.
Hm?!
So what other kinds
of future ninjutsu
are there?
[chuckles]
Future ninjutsu, eh?
It is...
...all about
Space-style!
[gasp]
What is Space-style?
I gotta say, it sounds
futuristic and cool!
Oh believe me,
it is far beyond
cool!
You have my permission!
Show them, Kabuemon!
It is now time
for me to leave!
Are you kidding me!?
Oh man! I really can't
wait to see some
Space-style techniques!
If we learn how to use them
effectively the Hidden Leaf
will be nearly invincible!
This is so exciting!
Can you demonstrate
for us?
I can't just create a new
element out of the blue!
Well, now uh..
Space-style is..
it's.. uhh...
Hmm?
It's no good! I've got nothing!
All our hard work is about to
go up in flames!
Wait, Kabuemon!
I have an answer!
Oh uh?
Space is infinite.
Right?
So that means, even in faraway
places we cannot see from the
earth, there are stars shining
brightly in the darkness!
So when you think about
it, that means space is
the future!
Um.. oh yes, precisely.
Good analysis, Lee!
Huh?
Whaa?
I realize that the future
holds infinite potential.
Let us go, my friend
to the other end of
the time tunnel!
[yanked yelp]
Hey, get back
here, Lee!
Oh no! They're coming out
here! I'll have to invoke
a genjutsu!
Ha!
Huh?
You mean this
is the future?
The whole thing
seems very weird.
So! Welcome
to the future!
Hm?!
I ate so much ramen
over the years, it
made me obese, ya know!
That's my
future?!
I found another
wrinkle today!
That cannot
be me!
My heavens!
You boys are
cute!
Excuse me, but why
am I an old woman?!
[flirty moan]
[gasp]
And I am the future
version of Orochimaru!
[laughing]
Hey, how come you're
the only one who looks
futuristic?!
The future you is
still up to no-good!
It is not my past self's
fault that my future self
is a loser.
The only way to save the
future is to defeat the man
who controls it, which appears
to be Future Orochimaru!
I am going to need
your help Kabuemon!
What?!
Let us
do this!
Huh?!
You have
no chance!
[growls]
Stand still, you!
Why are you waiting,
Kabuemon?
Remember your training!
It is time to use the Rasengan!
Uhh...
Hurry!
R- right!
Rasengan!
Forgive me, Lord Orochimaru!
But you did say to maintain
my position as his friend,
at any cost!
Here we go!
Right!
Super Move!
Double Rasengan!
Wha--?
What's going on,
Kabu--?
Noooo!
We seem to be back in the past!
Do you have any idea what
actually happened here?
Whats going on?
Grilled fish heads I know
these are your favorites!
So dig right in, my friend!
Oh, thank you
so much, Lee!
Kabuemon, I cannot wait
until our next adventure!
You are definitely one of
my best friends!
Friends!
I like the
sound of that!
Hmm.
And so, in spite of the
incredible odds, Kabuto's
valiant effort has finally paid
off, and his plan is a success!
However, nothing in
this life goes as
smoothly as one hopes.
Kabuemon?
Yes, Lee...
[gasp]
A zipper?
Uh, oh!
Well, this
is awkward!
Next time on Rock Lee,
'Shino Loves Insects', and
'Tenten Fights A Maiden's
Battle'!
(Orochimaru)
Oh, yuck!
No, not bugs!
(Kabuto)
What are you so afraid of?
Earlier, I saw you squashing
them with your bare hands!
Hey, don't give the audience
that information! You're going
to screw with my agenda!
This is my
'Show-the-new-viewers-
another-side-of-Orochimaru
and-get-more-popular' plan!
I have no idea what's
going on in your head
these days.