The cherry blossoms are falling,
the birds are singing, the
weather is perfect...
...nature is glowing a vibrant
green! And I'm out of breath.
[Loud Inhale]
It is time for the sports meet!
And now, here to read the pledge
of good sportsmanship is our
own Rock Lee!
I pledge!
I can't believe they picked
Bushy Brow...
Oh, you're just jealous that
he's the center of attention.
No I'm not! I'm just envious
it's not me!
Do you really think he's going
to make it through the whole
pledge?
Well he better! I spent all day
yesterday helping him memorize
it! He should be fine...
We...we are uh...we uh...uhh...
He's totally blanking!
Umm...Uhh...
Come on, Lee!
You spent all day on
this, think!
We, we uhh...
We are...we are...we are
uh...Uh, we are here right...?
We are here today!
[Sighs]
He finally remember.
To celebrate our graduation!
[Cheering]
[Grunts]
This isn't a high school
graduation!
[Screaming]
[Explosion Sounds]
"The Leaf Village Sports Meet."
[Sigh] I completely
messed that up...
And I practiced so hard!
It's okay. It happens
sometimes.
Yes, don't let it get
to you.
That is it!
I will just have to redeem
myself by coming in first in
every single event today!
I think he let it
get to him...
I know you're upset, but you're
getting too worked up, even for
you!
Of course I am worked up! It is
what I do! But this is not just
about reclaiming my honor!
This meet has really got my
blood pumping extra hard!
It is a competition to show off
your athleticism, strength, and
bikini briefs!
Yes, you're right Lee. But at
the same time, you're so very,
very wrong.
Since I cannot use ninjutsu, a
sports competition...
...is the perfect venue for me
to demonstrate my skills!
So I have to succeed here,
no matter what!
[Grunts]
Stop focusing your power in
your bottom!
Remember, if you put too much
mental pressure on yourself...
...then you'll be too nervous
to succeed.
Yes that's right!
[Grunts]
Huh?
If you strain yourself too much,
you'll only be able to use half
your strength, Lee.
So what should I do then?
Simple, you don't sweat it!
I know better than anyone how
hard you try.
You've been running at my side
for a long time now.
But when you run together, your
hard work just turns into random
weirdness!
Just have faith in yourself! If
you go into this with your usual
focus, you'll win for sure!
Remember that, no matter what
may happen!
Yes! I will remember!
Hold up!
Huh?!
You're not even wearing the
right outfits!
Idiot! Idiot!
So, have you finally calmed
down now Lee?
Yes! I'm loose and relaxed!
A little too loose.
if you asked me!
I am going to sweep this entire
competition, just you watch me!
I will not even let you two
beat me, either!
Talking big again, huh? Well, it
looks like you're back to
normal, Lee.
Yeah, but is that
good or bad?
Our first event is going
to be the foot race!
Have faith in myself...
If I stay confident, I will
succeed!
On your marks...Get set...
Whoa! No way!
Sometime today, Kakashi Sensei!
[Gun Shot]
[Grunts]
I am not done yet!
[Screaming]
Huh?
Coming through, Bushy Brow!
No come back here!
[Screaming]
I am still not done yet!
Ahh! [Embarrassed Laugh]
[Grunting]
The winner is Naruto!
I am still not done yet!
Huh?
I will win, I will lose. I will
win, I will lose.
You totally rock, Naruto!
I mean you're completely
cleaning up in this meet!
Yay me!
Honestly though, it was more
luck than anything.
Huh?! Hey, it wasn't luck at
all! I'm just that good! Watch,
I'm gonna win this whole thing!
[Lee Mumbling]
You're letting this get to you
too much.
[Lee Mumbling]
Are you okay, Lee?
I will lose...
This cannot be happening.
Guy Sensei told me that if I
just had confidence, I would win
for sure!
Knock it off, you're
being annoying!
Champion, Champion, I'm
number one!
Naruto!
Huh?
Uh, Bushy Brow?
You okay?
I am still not done yet.
I swear...I swear that I...
I will defeat you Naruto!
[Grunts]
If you think you've got what it
takes then bring it on!
Our next competition is just
about to begin! It's the
scavenger hunt!
Each competitor will draw from
the box a card with an item
written on it.
They'll then have to find and
borrow that item from someone.
The first person to cross the
goal with their item wins!
Lady Tsunade, tell us: what do
you think the key is to winning
a race like this?
Just pure luck...
There you have it!
Will Naruto continue his string
of victories? Will Rock Lee win
his challenge to the current
leader?
Will a new front-runner emerge?
Is anyone even listening?
On your marks...
There is no way I am going to
lose to this time, Naruto!
Let's do it, Bushy Brow!
Let's just stay calm and move
apart, you guys.
Get set...Woah!
[Bang!]
And they're off!
Don't forget about me!
Neji Hyuga takes an early lead!
He's got his card! But it seems
that something is wrong...
"A somewhat melancholy..."
"Ghost?!"
What a shocking item for him to
have to find! How will he handle
it?
I'm not going to let this
obstacle defeat me!
Eight Trigrams Rotation!
Where are you going, Neji?!
It appears that Neji has just
exited the arena in order to go
see if he can find a ghost!
Lady Tsunade, in your opinion,
what would you say went wrong
for Neji in this event?
Just bad luck.
There you have it!
Sakura's about to draw her card
now!
Oh boy, I hope that I get
something easier!
'A fleeting dream within a
dream."
She's picked a very lightweight
item!
How the heck do I find something
like this?!
These competitors find
themselves utterly stumped
by their difficult items!
It seems that Lady Tsunade's
analysis was correct: it all
comes down to luck!
God, Buddha, Great Spaghetti
Monster...whoever is listening,
please grant me luck!
It seems neither God nor
anyone else heard! The card says
"sweet devil!"
Hey, wasn't that a song in the
70's?
I do not have time to track down
a copy of that song!
But I cannot let Naruto win this
event!
Maybe my card will give me a
way to help Lee somehow...
Tenten has made her pick...
"A thrilling conclusion where
your best friend's defeat makes
you snap and awakens your latent
powers!"
Wait, that's been done before.
This isn't a scavenger hunt,
it's a silly mess, and I don't
want to mess around with it
anymore!
You okay, Lee?
What is that ?!
And now, for the
second stage...
How did you draw that
summoning circle so fast?!
All that I have to do is dial
the number listed here!
What?! You can't just summon
devils over the phone!
Yes, hello there. I am over at
the sports stadium for the
competition today.
Could you please send over a
devil right away?
[Tenten Angrily Screaming]
All you have to do is head
toward downtown and make a right
turn on Shuuei...
All right, I'm gonna finish
Bushy Brow off right now!
Huh?
Uhh...
Naruto seems to be confused by
what's written on his card.
Hmm.
Huh?
What is it, Naruto?
Well, uh...This is hard to say
but I kinda sorta need to borrow
something from you, Sakura...
"Find the girl who stole your
heart on that fateful day..."
...and borrow her...
What?!
I really only need to borrow
them for a minute...
Huh?
[Screams]
[Gasps]
Uh...medic?
Ooh, cliffhanger! What did that
paper say?!
"Chicken Fights Are Part of the
Thrill of Youth."
[Grunting]
Okay. Yeah.
The scavenger hunt's been called
off due to injury...
...and because all anyone found
are reasons to complain.
[Grunting]
Sorry I hit you.
The real problem was all the
weird stuff we had to find, not
your injury.
It's only my head.
Next we'll begin the red versus
white cheerleading competition!
What? Cheerleading?!
I have to win the next one! I
will win! There is no doubt! I
will win for sure!
What is wrong with winning? Is
there a law against it? I do not
think so! Although I guess I
should check...
Maybe it would help Lee get back
on track if I cheered him on...
[Cheering]
Wahhoo! Yeah!
But I don't know...I'd be so
embarrassed to wear a
cheerleading uniform!
Hmm...
But you know what! I'll do it
for Lee!
[Cheering]
[Cheering] Go! Go! White team
go!
No this is wrong I'm having
doubts about this!
Fight! Fight! White team fight!
Totally, you know?!
Thats definitely wrong, no
doubt about it!
Hooray! Hooray! Red team go!
Aw, thanks, Sajura! You rock!
I will do my best
too, Sakura!
What are you getting all pumped
up for?! They're cheering for
the other team!
I am sorry, Tenten!
We're about to move on to our
next event! Time for the
tug-of-war to begin!
Unlike team tug-of-war
competitions, these will be
one-on-one matches.
Does our color commentator, Lady
Tsunade have any insight on how
to win this one?
Have good luck.
There you have it...
Are you ready for
this Lee?
Of course I am!
Because Guy Sensei told me that
if I just believe in myself, I
will win for sure!
Okay, but in case it doesn't go
that way, try to remember...
...if you need anything, I'm
right here.
Thank you, but I am fine!
I will show everyone that
I can win on my own!
Uh, great!
[Chuckling]
Go.
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
Incredible! It looks like Rock
Lee and Naruto are evenly
matched!
Wait! Lee has taken a small
lead!
Oh no you don't! Sexy Jutsu!
Hi!
[Screaming]
That's a dirty move by Naruto!
Which is exactly why it's so
effective.
Fine! I will counter with my own
ninjutsu!
You mean with your delusion!
You can't use that!
[Screams]
Wait, you just changed
your clothes!
I'd say it's time to
wrap this up!
Naruto makes a bold move with
the Shadow clone Jutsu to end
this fast!
Why didn't he just use that to
start with?
Got you Bushy Brow!
Oh, no! I refuse to lose this!
'Scuse me...
Huh?!
[Gasp] It is here!
What?!
What is that?
A Mr. Rock Lee placed an order
for a devil. Could you please
tell me where to find him?
Uh, that would be me.
Oh! I apologize for
misunderstanding master.
Please tell me how may I be of
service to you.
Well, to start with you can help
me with this tug-of-war.
Understood, Master.
You've got it!
The sweet devil joins in! And
Naruto's having a devil of a
time keeping up!
Lee's coming back from
the brink of defeat!
Hey, wait a second! Isn't this
supposed to be a one-on-one
tug-of-war?
Yes, but to play devil's
advocate, technically Naruto was
the first one to break the
rule.
Forget the rules! That's a
devil, for crying out loud!
We have to keep things on this
show in-universe!
What's your analysis, Lady
Tsunade?
The rule does state
that this tug-of-war must be
one-on-one.
They lucked out.
[Sigh] There you have it!
Woah, this is insane! All right,
I'll just have to win with brute
force then!
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
[Screams]
What a turn of events! Both
competitors go flying!
The decision about who the
victor will be now rests with
the referee!
Huh?
Kakashi Sensei!
Who won?
Oh...uh...sorry I wasn't
paying attention.
[Grunts]
And on that note, it's time for
us to break for lunch!
Here, Lee. Why don't you eat
something?
No, thank you. I am trying to
stay in the zone.
Okay, well how about a shoulder
rub? You must be pretty beat.
Right now, I have to stay
focused on finding a way to win.
Lunches and shoulder rubs are
only going to distract me from
that.
Listen, it's fine to put the
competition first...
...but you really don't have to
do everything on your own, you
know?
I do not understand.
This is my battle.
I guess, but you're
not alone...
The time has come for
our final event!
You guessed it, it's the
chicken fight!
In this event, teams of four
will duke it out, trying to
take their opponents hat...
...or knock them off their
teammates' shoulders. The last
group standing wins!
Lady Tsunade, what are your
thoughts? What's the key to
winning a competition like this?
It's all luck.
Really? You don't say? A very
astute observation.
[Screaming]
[Screams]
That's not a chicken!
It's a horse!
Nice, huh? I stayed up all
night making it!
Hop on in here and you'll feel
just like a thoroughbred, I
guarantee it!
Where is Neji, anyway? We need
four people to compete in this
event.
There's no time. The two of us
will have to do it.
What! Oh, why do you guys always
make me do stuff like this!?
[Cheering]
Now Lee, we're one person short,
so you've got to keep things
under control.
I do not think so.
What?!
This is the final battle! No
matter what it takes, I must
defeat Naruto all by myself!
You do know that we're carrying
you, right?
Everyone hold on tight,
and...go.
Let's do this!
Charge!
Do the other thing!
Retreat!
[Horse Noises]
Uh, oh! It's trouble for Lee!
His team is down a member, his
costume's the wrong animal...
...and he's been surrounded! I
mean, seriously, can his team do
anything right?
Okay! You don't have
to rub it in!
I have got this.
Hidden Leaf Un, Deux, Trois!
[Chuckles]
Hey, where were you
hiding that tutu?!
Hornet Stinger!
I'm gonna hurl!
Quick! Knock him off their
shoulders!
[Grunts]
Where'd their horse go? What?
Hmph! I just used the
substitution Jutsu!
Good one, Guy Sensei!
Come on! You just jumped out of
the costume!
Depantsification Jutsu!
Don't do that!
Keep it up, Lee. You're doing a
great job! Show these guys what
you've got!
Yeah but you don't have to show
them Guy Sensei!
So it has come to this. Leaf
Crapshoo-Ahh!
No, not that!
[Screams]
[Grunting]
Are you nuts, trying to use Leaf
Crapshoot while you're standing
on our shoulders?!
I am sorry.
Do you understand now, Lee?
Do I understand what?
It appears that you're finally
starting to use your true
strength.
But do you know what
that really is?
True strength...?
You've been trying to fight on
your own this entire day.
It's understandable. There are a
lot of solo events at these
kinds of meets.
But it's right when you're
fighting alone that you need the
support of your friends behind
you more than ever!
The support of my friends? But
what do you mean by that?
Cue the flashback...
Just have faith in yourself! If
you go into this with your usual
focus you'll win for sure!
Remember that no matter
what may happen!
Haven't you figured out what I'm
trying to tell you?
When do you feel like you have
the most confidence in yourself,
Lee?
When I am with my friends!
That's it! So, you think you can
beat Naruto?
Yes!
Hmm.
This is it, folks. The battle's
entering its final round.
It's Lee versus Naruto,
winner take all!
It's all luck.
I didn't even ask you
this time.
The cheers have reached a fever
pitch! It's down to the final
two! Who will emerge victorious?
Bring it on, Naruto!
All right!
[Cheering]
He is strong! I would expect
nothing less!
[Grunt]
Lee!
Ha! I've got you now,
Bushy Brow!
Woah!
Lee is inches away
from defeat!
[Grunting] I will not
lose! Not now!
I cannot disappoint the friends
who have supported me every
step of the way today!
Sorry I'm so late.
Huh?
Wait, that voice!
Neji!
Incredible! Out of nowhere, Neji
has reappeared with his
scavenger hunt item...
...a somewhat melancholy ghost!
[Sigh]
[Screams]
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
Ouch, that really hurt!
Oh!
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Unbelievable! Lee wins! Neji,
completely oblivious to the
dramatic atmosphere...
...has propelled Lee to a huge
comeback victory!
[Cheering]
Good job. You got me
this time, Lee.
Thanks, Naruto.
But the next time we meet,
I'm gonna win!
We gotta make sure it's a true
one-on-one battle, though!
Yes, so we can see who truly
is the best. But can we still
have friends cheer for us?
Yeah, you bet! I want our
friends to be there too!
I'm happy for you Lee.
I'm glad you beat Naruto.
Thanks, but it was not just me!
We all won together!
[Giggles]
Friends are wonderful, aren't
they, Lee? They just make
everything better.
Yes!
As we run through the days
ahead, we must always remember
to cherish our friends!
Now, follow me!
Right Guy Sensei!
Wait up, I'm coming too!
Me too!
Huh?
Me too...
Hey! How many friends
does one guy need?!
Ouch!
Idiot! Idiot!
In this week's horoscopes, the
worst is a type-A Sagittarius.
"You're highly susceptible to
bad luck. Avoid all contact with
type-B Scorpios."
Lee, aren't you a type-A
Sagittarius?
I do not believe in
horoscopes- Ah! A bird
pooped on my head!
Next week, "Orochimaru is a
Type-B Scorpio." and "Love
Letters are the Ultimate Trap."
[Screams] Oh, no! I just
stepped in dog poop!
Hey, guys, wait up!
[Crash] Ow! Where did this
washbasin come from...?!