We open in a certain
mountain town.
The atmosphere
here is quite odd
and unnerving...
Well, looks like
we made it in.
Yeah.
As long as we continue
to keep a low profile,
we should be able to
track down this illegal
chakra-trading ring, and
arrest the perpetrators.
Ah-ha! "We made it in."
"A low profile." This
must be an undercover
operation.
Any idea what
happened to Lee?
Was he able to
sneak in, too?
I don't know.
I haven't seen
him.
(Rock Lee)
Tenten! Neji!
There you are!
Looks like we all
managed to sneak in!
You didn't sneak in
You stick out like a
big sore thumb! Huh?
17 Nights of Staying
Out of Sight
We were really lucky that
Guy Sensei and the others
were right there to back
us up when they did.
With you drawing so much
unwanted attention, I wasn't
sure what was gonna happen!
Sorry. When did it all start
going so wrong? I was sure I
I had the perfect cover for
the mission.
Are you kidding?!
You couldn't have
been more obvious!
Lee innately stands
out in pretty much
every situation.
So I stand out, do I?
Hmm, I suppose...
The show is in its
fourth season now...
If my presence did
not carry so much
weight and gravitas..
..then I would not have
survived as a prime
time TV character for
a whole year!
Yeah, sorry.
That's not the
real issue here.
But Neji's theory that
you naturally stand out
could certainly mean
a lot of trouble.
Huh? What do you
mean by that?
Think about it
for a second.
Mission or not, the core of
being a ninja is concealing
yourself. It's never okay to
draw attention to yourself.
It goes against
everything you
represent.
I see what
you mean.
Especially considering
I am one who cannot
use jutsu.
If I am standing
out instead of staying
undercover, like I should...
Then this is a
fatal weakness!
Yes! Understood!
I will work my tail off
to erase every trace of
my conspicuousness!
[yells]
No, no, no!
That hot-blooded
enthusiasm is at the
root of the problem!
Lee! Get
back here!
Lee, wait!
[chuckling]
Kabuto. Did you
hear what I just
heard?
I sure did.
I admit, Lee certainly
is in the top tier of
conspicuous characters
on the show.
Honestly, I'd put you
one level above him,
Lord Orochimaru.
Speaking from my
wealth of experience..
..it's obvious that Lee is
going to do some kind of
special training regimen to
learn to erase his presence.
And speaking from my
wealth of experience..
..it's obvious that
you're going to try
and interfere with
that at every turn.
[snickers]
If I can sabotage his
training long enough..
..even his inexhaustible
positivity will eventually
crumble.
"It is hopeless.
I am not fit to
be a ninja!"
The fool. I can hear
his pathetic uncontracted,
whining now!
Try not to to be so
positive about it,
Lord Orochimaru.
With his annoying
self-confidence
eradicated, Lee will
be easily defeated.
I just don't get it.
Why can't you see that if you
acted like you do in the main
series, you could defeat Lee
any time you wanted.
Very soon, Rock Lee
is going down!
(Rock Lee)
Then it hit me.
If I could just get
Sai to help, he could
train me in the art of
blending in.
Nice! Good
thinking.
With Sai being
from the ANBU..
..it makes sense that hiding
his presence and blending in
with the background would be
his specialties.
I appreciate the praise
and your faith in me. But
I'm not sure anyone could
help you become inconspicuous.
Please, Sai!
I am begging you!
Help me!
All right.
Let's see
here...
I want you to picture
these situations in
your mind...
A boy who always
sits in the back
of the class...
Who disappears from
the classroom during
breaks...
And walks home
from school all
by himself.
Got it! So I need
to put myself in
that kind of mindset.
I will use my
specialty genjutsu!
You mean skits.
Always sit in the
back corner, check!
Disappear from the
classroom during
breaks, check!
And walk home from
school all by myself,
check-checkity-check!
How did I do, Sai?
Well Your vigorous recreation
of those scenarios makes you
even more conspicuous than
usual.
This is utterly and
completely hopeless!
If my genjutsu does
not work, what else
will help me understand?
Imagine this,
instead...
Tenshinmen, a crab omelet
with gravy over noodles, on
a Chinese restaurant menu.
It's positioned all the way
on the end, forgotten, to the
point where you think, "Has
anyone ever even ordered that?"
Oh, I see. No one who came
in wanting ramen would order
tenshinmen. They would not
consider it.
And if they wanted crab
and eggs, they would
probably just go with
a crab omelet instead.
So tenshinmen basically
has no real presence on a
Chinese menu. I've never
thought of it that way.
I just need to
understand how
tenshinmen feels!
How am I
doing, Sai?
Poorly. Again, you fail
for unnaturally recreating
the scenario.
[yells]
Blending in with the crowd
and not reacting to anything
are what make you inconspicuous.
The less attention you
draw to yourself, the
better.
Ah, I see...
Start by wearing only ordinary,
everyday clothing. Avoid unusual
attire.
That business suit might be
what normal people wear. But
nobody wears stuff like that
in this show's universe!
Next, you must learn to
control your reactions
no matter what the
situation is.
I don't know what universe
you're in, but this situation
is completely out of control!
[sigh]
Even though I realize this is
part of your training, I feel
disturbed that you can simply
chose to ignore me.
And why in the world
is Neji upset about it?
Oh, the humanity! I had no
idea masking one's presence
was such a painful process!
It's painful, alright.
It hurts me just to
watch this mess.
And so, Sai's strange
training and lessons
continued.
Your final task lies right over
there. You must eat a meal at
that soba restaurant, alone,
without anyone noticing you.
What?
But that's
so normal.
Exactly. Acting like a normal
person is how we'll make him
stop standing out.
Go for it, Lee!
Good luck!
Welcome! I'm afraid
you'll have to share
a table.
One soba
with eggs.
Coming
right up.
One with eggs!
[devious laughing]
Just you wait, Lee.
Your frenetic efforts to mask
your presence and blend in
with the crowd around you...
...are going to be ruined by
none other than yours truly!
I get it.
Lord Orochimaru is going to be
even more anonymous than Lee,
right in his face.
He is even more anonymous
than me! I have lost this
battle!
Nothing could be more
humiliating for him in
this situation.
[devious laughing]
Now, observe and despair!
Prepare to meet your doom!
Huh?
[slurping]
(Lord Orochimaru)
Huh? What's
going on here?
(Kabuto)
How strange. Lee
isn't reacting at
all.
Oh noooo!
Wait! Of course!
Orochimaru cannot get the better
of Lee unless Lee first realizes
that he is in fact Orochimaru!
And to do that...
He'll have to do something
to stand out, ruining the
anonymity contest in the
process!
I didn't realize that.
So this is what it means
to be hoisted by your own
petard!
You've been hoisted
clear across the planet!
[groans]
This is driving me crazy!
I want him to notice I'm
here! Notice me, senpai!
You can't, Lord Orochimaru! It
would defeat the entire purpose
of coming here! Everything would
be for naught!
Meanwhile,
Lee is thinking...
Huh. What is
Orochimaru
doing here?
Ah.. he did notice.
Normally...
Orochimaru! What are you
doing here?! Answer me!
Or something
like that.
Reacting makes you
stand out. You must
control yourself.
Sai was very clear
on that point.
[groans]
[yelling]
I want to react so bad!
But I cannot! What do
I do?! What do I do?!
I want him to notice me so bad!
But I can't make him! What do I
do?! What do I do?!
[yelling]
This'll be a big risk,
but it's my only option!
What are you going to
do, Lord Orochimaru?!
[gasp]
Pardon me. May I
use the seasoning?
No freakin' way! He didn't
notice even me when I asked
him for the shichimi?
In this situation, that was
a borderline illegal move, and
it still didn't work?! I don't
get it!
Why doesn't he
notice me?!
I want to
react so
badly!
[slurping]
I cannot take
it anymore!
(Naruto)
Hello there!
Huh?
One tempura
soba, please!
Huh?
Bushy-brows and Orochimaru?
Why're you guys dressed like
a couple of businessmen?
Uh...
No reason...
[slurping]
[sigh]
And so, Lee and Orochimaru
learned just how difficult
it can be to go unnoticed
and blend in with the crowd.
What about this?
I can hide my presence by
making everyone else even
more outlandish than me!
Genius!
This is so wrong.
Well?
I definitely don't
stand out as much
like this.
You know, something
tells me we'll never
get back ontrack.
[laughing]
It appears there is
still a long road ahead.
The bathroom, the kitchen,
the laundry room. So many
rooms we use day in and
day out.
But the most important
one of all is...
The bathroom?
Yes, that's right. Lately
people have been leaving
the public bathroom a
complete mess.
Graffiti,
poor hygiene,
disgraceful.
That's why you're here.
Your mission is to clean the
bathroom from top to bottom.
I want it shiny and spotless..
..I'm counting
on you!
Right!
Cleaning the Bathroom
Cleanses the Soul!
Good, you're all here.
I trust you understand how
important this mission is?
Yes, of course!
As the old saying goes,
"everything begins and
ends with the toilet."
That's not it at all!
It's "everything begins
and ends with family!"
Keeping things clean and
tidy is just basic common
sense. It is easy!
[pained yell]
You fool!
Why'd you hit him?
Listen up, Lee!
Keeping the bathroom spotless
and clean is the exact same
thing as keeping your soul
spotless and clean, understand?
As you scrub and disinfect the
toilet, think of it as polishing
and perfecting your skills!
You don't have to force
the metaphor anymore!
I had no idea that cleaning
the bathroom was so meaningful!
I have been such a fool, Guy
Sensei!
It's okay.
You understand
now.
[crying]
Yeah, yeah,
now can we please
get to work already?
And so, the team cleaned the
bathrooms until they were
spotless and shiny. But then...
(Guy)
Wait, what?
You mean they're
all filthy again?
We did such a good
job yesterday.
It's crazy.
I can't believe
it got this bad
in one night.
I don't get it.
What could've
happened?
Hmm...
[laughing]
Everything went
according to plan.
Ah. These two,
of course.
Who else?
We'll mess up the
Leaf's bathroom!
That's my latest
ingenious plan.
..Rumors will spread
about how disgusting
and filthy they are.
Fewer and fewer people
will come to the village..
Eventually, people
will leave this place
all together.
..And the Leaf will be
on the path to ruin!
Lord Orochimaru's imagination
is the only thing on the path
to ruin.
In this plan, everything
begins and ends with the
toilet.
[chuckles]
Now! Scream in
despair, fools!
What should we do
now, Guy Sensei?
Well, there's always
the chance that this
could just be some
kind of evil prank.
Right! The plan is to
guard this place and
see if we can uncover
the truth. Got it?
Got it!
Oh no! Regardless of how good
or bad the plan is, if they
start setting up watch and
guarding the place,
Lord Orochimaru won't
have an opportunity
to carry it out!
[chuckles]
Gotta pee,
gotta pee!
Whew! Didn't think
I was gonna make it!
[sigh]
Impossible. Sakura,
how could you?
Lady Hinata.
No way!
Why're you two so
depressed? Did you
think they were
above this?
It's never easy for a
man to accept reality.
Sometimes the truth rips
through to the soul.
What's that
supposed to
mean?!
Anyways, Naruto, Sakura,
and Hinata all showed a
complete lack of manners,
so we know it's not a prank.
They're just
inconsiderate.
Hm..
Really? That's incredible!
Lord Orochimaru didn't have
to do anything?
Everyone in the Leaf's
just gross and leaves
a huge mess behind?
Elementary,
my dear Kabuto.
Being the true genius
that I am, I created
the "Mess up the Leaf
Bathroom" jutsu..
..a terrifying mind-control
technique that perfectly
complements my plan!
Whoa! You created a
mind-control jutsu?!
It's like this, anyone
under its influence will
be compelled to leave the
bathrooms a complete mess!
Pretty amazing,
wouldn't you agree?
Incredible!
If he can really do
something as amazing
as mind control..
..then why is he wasting time
with this bathroom plot and not
planning something significantly
bigger?!
Normally I'd yell at him, but
I'm too impressed with Lord
Orochimaru! He's on to something
with this one!
And that's not
the end of it.
[gasp]
It not only leaves the bathroom
a disgusting mess that must be
cleaned over and over..
..but by giving Lee and his
pals a harsh dose of reality,
it sends them into a deep
depression, too!
When a man is forced to
acccept the reality tha
even his perfect little
idols must take a 'idiot'..
..it sends their minds
into a fiery hell from
which there is no return!
[laughing]
This is so cool! I mean,
what he's saying is kinda
messed up and demented..
..but he hasn't been
this on the ball since
the series began!
(Rock Lee)
No! Impossible!
Huh?
Sakura does not-
Sakura does not drop
'idiot'! I refuse to
accept that!
I really don't see
why you have to get
so worked up about
all this.
He's right! Lady Hinata
would never ever take a
'idiot'! It's beneath her!
Come on!
Not you,
too!
Sakura and Hinata
are not behind this!
It must be someone else!
Huh? But we saw them go
in and out. We confirmed
it just moments later.
It is not like them.
I feel the culprit
must be him!
Yes, I agree, Lee.
I was just thinking
only he could be behind
something so diabolical.
Huh?
"He" who?
Who do
you think?
It is Orochimaru,
for sure!
Whaaaat?!
Knowing him, he must have
created some kind of new
jutsu that makes the victim
want to mess up the bathroom.
Exactly.
What else would explain
Sakura taking a huge
'idiot'?!
That's right! Neither
she nor Lady Hinata
could possibly 'idiot'!
[groans]
We underestimated
their delusional
tendencies.
They're so determined not to
face reality that even with
absolutely no evidence, they're
blaming Lord Orochimaru.
And on top of that, they
made up an excuse that
happens to be his exact
plan!
This is just like, when a girl
with a difficult personality
who isn't popular with boys
says something like...
I just can't seem to
find myself a boyfriend.
It's weird, right?
It must be because
they're all too nervous
and afraid to ask me out.
Completely missing the point,
yet at the same time, absolutely
correct! It's the exact same
situation!
Wh- What do we do,
Lord Orochimaru?
Everything's
fine, Kabuto.
Huh?!
It doesn't matter that
those idiots were lucky
enough to figure out my
jutsu.
They still have no
way of stopping it.
The only thing they can
possibly do is sit back
and watch their bathrooms
be ruined..
..knowing there's nothing
they can do about it.
[chuckles]
However, a few
days later...
I see...
So the bathroom problem is
solved, then? It looks like
Team Guy did a good job on
this one.
..Maybe I'll give them
a bonus for a job well
done.
Uh Wait, what
did she say?
The bathrooms
aren't dirty?
Impossible!
That can't
be true!
Could the jutsu
have somehow
lost its effect?
You mean some sort
of stupid oversight?
That's so contrived it
sounds like something
right out of a comedy
anime..
..where they completely
make up terrible reasons
for the villain to fail
just to end the episode!
That's exactly what usually
happens to us, but I'll bite
my tongue this time around.
I added a special ingredient
to the jutsu that causes the
effects to continue on for a
whole month.
We'll just have to
see what's happening
for ourselves.
Make way!
Gotta pee,
gotta pee.
Everything seems
to be good so far.
Easy!
No running!
Huh?!
Huh?
Now listen here,
Ms. Toilet.
This school has a long,
celebrated history of
producing gentle,
refined women!
Every one of our students
toils day in and day out to
become pretty, well-mannered
household fixtures..
..so that they can
graduate and proudly
function in society.
You need get your
priorities together
and start acting like
you belong here!
Ew, I don't want
to be near Toilet.
She's so gross.
She's all dirty
and nasty.
[laughing]
Ma! Why do I
have to be a
toilet?!
Why couldn't I be born
clean and pretty, like
Ms. Sink or Ms. Bathtub?
It is not fair!
My dear child, within every
single toilet there is a
beautiful porcelain god.
If you keep the toilet
clean, you keep your
soul clean, too.
Understand?
It cleans..
your soul, too?
Don't worry about silly
outward appearances.
You grow up to be a
toilet with a beautiful
soul, okay?
Ma...
After that day, I made it
a point to start being nice
to everyone I meet, no matter
what.
Even if they bullied me,
insulted me, or were rude
to me in any way, I was
nice to them all the same.
To help make
myself beautiful.
Today, things are a lot
different than they were
back then. I'm dating an
amazing five-star hotel.
He says the thing he
loves most about me
is my beautiful soul.
I feel like if people
learn to keep the toilet
clean, anyone can be
beautiful.
[crying]
Oh, man! What an
emotional story!
I'll make sure to
leave the bathroom
clean from now on!
[crying]
Damn them!
They used a clever
genjutsu against me!
Lord Orochimaru,
that was just a skit.
Fine then!
They leave me
no choice!
Huh?
Orochimaru?!
He's gonna try
to mess up the
bathroom!
If you want something done
right, do it yourself!
Huh? What the..
This feels like...
It can't be...
Could it be?
A water-style
jutsuuuuuooohoooo.
Phew.
Huh?
You win.
Lord Orochimaru, wait!
And so, with Kakashi's
chakra powering the
water-style jutsu..
Orochimaru was moved
beyond words to a
state of clean euphoria.
[laughing]
The next episode is "The Staff
Will Eat the Beans Afterwards!"
and "The Raikage is Under
Attack!"
Lord Orochimaru,
the Raikage is
being targeted.
I think maybe we should
start with the Hidden
Cloud and then move on
to the Leaf-
No!
I'm staying by the Leaf!
No matter what happens,
I will claim that bathroom
for myself!
Oh, come on.
You just want to
use that toilet
again.