Today we find ourselves
in the Hidden Sand
Village, far from the
Hidden Leaf.
There are other ninja
villages, too, but the
Leaf and the Sand are
especially close allies.
That's why Rock Lee and
his team are on their way
to the Hidden Sand right
now for a mission.
We should reach the
village any minute now.
Huh? What's
that cloud?
Ruuuuuun!
I want to be friends with
Gaara!
Oh, it's just you. I
thought you were enemy
shinobi.
In case you've been
living under a rock, this
is Gaara.
He's the
Kazekage, or leader,
of the Hidden Sand.
Gaara and Lee once met on
the field of battle.
Lee risked his safety to
use a forbidden jutsu,
but he still lost and
got really hurt in the
process.
Gaara. Hey! How nice
to see you again!
I think he can hear
your teeth chattering.
Yes, I may have lost when
we fought that one time,
but I have been
practicing a lot. Victory
is mine next time...
Anyway...
He ignored me!
I don't think he sees
you as a worthy opponent,
Lee.
He is Kazekage, after
all.
Don't get down
about it.
I guess I should tell
you why you're here.
Rumor has it rogue
ninjas have slipped
into the village.
I want you to route
these intruders out.
Indeed. You can count on
us, Gaara.
Wait, is Lee harboring a
grudge? I mean, Gaara did
hurt him pretty bad back
then,
and blew him
off today.
Lee's been staring at
him the whole time we've
been here.
[puckering]
Whoa, Lee! Back
it up!
Get your ugly mug away
from Gaara!
Ahhhh!
Temari! Kankuro!
These are Gaara's older
sister and brother, Temari
and Kankuro.
Maybe you know them,
but maybe not.
No funny stuff near
the Kazekage.
Back off.
Why are you mad at me?!
Your brother was the one
swooping in to steal my
first kiss!
That's enough!
What has gotten into you
today?! Tell Gaara
you're sorry, Lee!
Take heart. I will say
sorry with you.
Right.
My bad!
Yeah, what he said!
Those don't count! Those
were the worst apologies
I've ever heard!
Neither of you meant
a single word of it!
What the heck is
going on with Lee
today?
Indeed. He's really
pushing people's
buttons.
This isn't a good day
for him to get weird
on us.
Don't worry. Sensei's
got a solution.
Solution?
Welcome to the 138th
Annual Leaf vs. Sand
Alliance-Team Building
Barbecue Cook-Off, and
more! Thanks for coming,
everybody!
Why are we doing this,
again?
Don't you know?
No idea.
Barbecues are a summer
tradition! They're a
chance for young people
to come together,
overcook some low-grade
beef, and frolic along
the riverbank!
Is that supposed to be
fun? 'Cause I'm not
feeling it.
But wait, there's more!
Barbecues are also an
arena where dads can earn
the respect of their
wives and kids with
their fearless grilling
skills!
The way you describe
barbecues doesn't make
me wanna go to one!
The point is...
Barbecues give folks who
don't have a ton in
common, and don't
particularly like each
other the chance to get
along for a change!
I see. If all goes well,
Lee and Gaara will be
able to clear the air
between them.
Will you lend
a hand?
Do we have a choice?
And you're sure this is
gonna work?
Absolutely! I'm a
master of the grill!
Okay, everyone! The food
is ready!
Something's half-baked,
and it's not the cuts
of meat.
Lee, Gaara! Check out
these fire-sticks!
Crazy, huh?!
I give it about a
minute before he burns
himself with one of those.
Lee! Gaara! Look at that
roast pig! You know you
want a piece! What are
you waiting for?!
He's going way faster
than the pig.
I think we know where
the real ham is here and
it's not in the spit.
No change yet.
Usually, he'd be up for
whatever foolishness Guy
Sensei pulled.
Pig didn't work.
Obviously this is bad.
Let's go bigger!
Let's dance! Kick up
your heels and trip the
light fantastic! Shake
it, you guys!
So we're ditching the
barbecue for a festival?!
This is not the time for
a dance number!
Why not?
How's their village
still standing?
Oh, man.
[screaming]
Huh?
[grunting]
[snickering]
That's the last of 'em.
Time to tear this dumb
village up!
[chuckling]
Here they come!
You're a rogue ninja
attacking my village?
When we fight I will
defeat far more of these
villains than you!
He's still hung up on
Gaara at a time like
this?!
This time, I shall win!
Uh, Lee?! What are you
doing?!
Look, everybody! I am
faster than his sand!
[laughing]
Maybe this could wait
'til later?!
[grunting]
What's his problem?
'Bout to get worse!
Sand Coffin!
I can't move.
That is not so hard!
[gasping]
Sand Squeeze!
Why do you keep doing
that thing?!
Sand Shower!
[grunting]
Damn it!
Too easy!
Sweat Shower!
Stop it! That's
disgusting!
Eww! Yuck! That's
gross! Blech!
Everyone feels better
after a good, honest
sweat!
Only if it's their own
sweat! Not someone
else's!
I can't endanger the village
with big moves. I'll have
to just fight with the sand
in my gourd.
That's the spirit,
Lee! You can do it!
[struggling]
Gaara's sand attack
accidentally hit Lee!
[groaning]
Huh? Even though he
totally missed, he's so
calm about it!
Uh... sorry.
I take it back! He's
sweating like crazy! It's
coming right through his
sand armor!
Please. It is nothing
more than a scratch.
Hey! Who wrapped it?!
You should fall back. You
can't fight like that.
No...
What the?
Tell me. Why are
you doing this?
Yeah, Lee. What do you
keep trying to one-up
Gaara for? You resent him
that much?
Tenten. I do not resent
Gaara. That is not what
this is.
Huh?
I got hurt so badly
during my match with
Gaara, I feared my days
as a ninja were over.
But then...
Giving up on your dreams
hurts worse than any
injury you can get.
Have the operation!
I was brought back for
the sake of following my
dream.
I do not want to lose to
Gaara. Not because I resent
him, but to follow through
with my ninja way!
If you work hard enough,
you can defeat even a
natural.
That is why I
cannot stand down!
So that's his angle.
I talk a big game, but in
all the time I have been
thinking about it, I have
never come up with a way
to surpass Gaara. Alas,
I may have to give up...
Oh, Lee.
I--I'm sorry I mistook
your resolve for simple
envy.
Guy Sensei.
I see my star pupil
grabbing life by the
horns. Oh, to be young
again!
What verve! An
inspiration to us all!
I'm definitely not
inspired by that outfit!
Guy Sensei!
I get it! Yes, of course!
Sand Coffin!
Leaf Sandstorm!
He took all the sand for
his attack!
[panicking]
At long last, Lee, you
are above Gaara!
You're right
about that!
He's definitely above
him right now!
I thank the Hidden Leaf
for its aid.
Honestly, we could not
have done it without you,
Gaara. I mean it when I
say you really are amazing!
That said, I made a vow
during the nice-guy pose.
So I will surpass you through
hard work eventually!
Someday, we shall fight
again!
All right. You got it.
It's a deal.
It is a deal, he
said! I will wait for
you forever, Gaara!
[grunting]
Stop crying on me!
Whoa!!!
What's wrong with
you, Lee?!
The line between rival
and creeper can be cloudy.
But Rock Lee did get a little
closer to Gaara today.
One day while passing
through the mountains on
the way home from a
mission...
Someone's coming this
way.
Make sure you greet
him properly. It's
mountaineering
etiquette.
In that case...
I am all
set, baby!
My card and cellphone are
at the ready!
I didn't say social
climber, Lee!
Baby, you've gotta
network if you wanna be
the next big thing!
In the business world,
it's all about who you
know!
All I wanted you to do
was say hi to him!
What?!
Hello there!
[screaming]
Huh?
The Rock Lee Impostor
Strikes!
Huh?
So he ran when he saw
Lee?
Uh-huh.
Also...
[panicking]
We passed through a town
a little while later, and
everybody panicked as
soon as they laid eyes on
me. I cannot imagine why.
I have always thought
myself to be very
pleasant.
They saw a shady-looking
dude go by, and got all
freaked out.
I am not shady in the
slightest, Naruto. I
have absolutely nothing
to hide!
You've got stuff to hide,
all right. And I don't think
that leaf is doing the best
job of it!
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
I figured it out.
An impostor?
Yes. Exactly.
Apparently, someone who
looks exactly like Lee
has been running amok,
doing terrible things to
the townsfolk.
Eh, I wouldn't
call them terrible...
They're more like
dumb grade-school
pranks, really.
But why go around
pretending to be
Bushy-Brows?
Of course! He's a
copycat.
For real?
Now that Rock Lee and
his Ninja pals have started
to capture a market share,
copycats are sure to
come out of the woodwork.
So it's a PR move?!
That is a slap in the
face to our staff! I do
not roll out of bed
looking like this!
People have to draw
this perfect hair!
Hair is not the point,
Lee!
I am going to give this
fake a piece of my mind.
I think I'm gonna give
him a piece of my fist.
Thank you for helping us.
This fake could be
tougher to find than
we're giving him credit
for... This calls for a
lot of concentration.
From what I've learned,
this guy is like Lee in
every single way.
Every single way, huh?
Just leave it to me!
Huh?!
Ohhh noooo!
Get back here, lady!
Nooooo!
Why am I always put
in this position?
Please! Someone! Anyone!
Help!
The boss wants you for
his girlfriend,
cutie-pie!
Now, let's see what
you're hiding under
that sash!
Oh, you bad man!
I get it! If this faker
is like you in every way,
he'll have to rescue
Neji. Good plan, Naruto!
I guess it's
tickle-time 'til
someone stops me!
Is that really
necessary?
That is enough of that,
you ruffian!
Oh, good! Lee has
come to save her!
My name is Rock Lee! It
is true I have no
ninjutsu at my command,
but I can still
defend the weak!
You weren't supposed to
take the bait, you
doofus!
I was drawn in by their
amazing acting! Please,
forgive me!
You totally blew your
cover!
Telling me that blew your
cover.
Don't talk back to me!
Okay.
Think we should help him?
That is enough of you,
you ruffian!
Huh?
Whoa, it's the fake!
My name is Sock Lee! It
is true, I have no
ninjutsu at my command,
but I can still
defend the weak!
The face is totally
wrong! And did he just
call himself Sock Lee?!
Whoa! I'm face-to-face
with the real thing here!
You're mad about the
whole copycat thing, huh!
That's right! You're ruining
Lee's reputation, you know.
That said, you look
nothing alike, so maybe
we can just--
He really is the spitting
image, huh!
Unbelievable!
You don't need byakugan
to see they're not the
same!
Hm?
Who put a mirror in front
of me?
Snap out of it, Lee! This
guy looks nothing like
yoooou!
Listen up! This fakery
has to stop!
Well, if that's the
case, time for some
backup!
Reji! Zenzen, now!
You're kidding me!
[giggling]
Not even close!
Hey, Boss-man, can you
cover me for a sec?
Seriously? You're making
a Reji-register joke?!
She doesn't look
anything like you,
Tenten!
Then stop staring.
So, I guess Zenzen is
banking on a similar name.
These two should have put
more into their
disguises!
Like here. These are way
too big. And this part.
This is too curvy.
Why do you have to point
everything out?!
Your teamwork is pretty
bad. Who can tell the
real from the fake?
First we'll beat you,
then we'll take your
reputations away.
Oh, no you don't.
In that case, let
us begin.
We're gonna put the
hurt on you four!
Copycat or not, no one
talks like that anymore!
Face the wrath of my
secret move!
Here we go, Lee.
I'll bet the two of you
use the same attacks!
[shrieking]
Lee doesn't have
anything like that
up his sleeve!
It's like something from
an old school anime!
[grunting]
Lee!
Not good.
Get up and
attack him!
Hit this copycat with
your best stuff, Lee! And
I'm sure you'll come out
victorious!
All right, then! Let us
see what you do with...
Extending punch!
[struggling]
A, that's not your
move. B, there was no
extension!
Hey, Boss... I put my
hair down. Do I look
like him?
That is not what we're
talking about!
Enough with the
reactions already...
Don't you tell
me to be calm!
Time to end this! Shimura
Death Strike!
[winding up]
[grunting]
How do ya like that?!
That had to hurt!
Yeah, no kidding! Even
watching that was
painful!
[grunting]
Victory is mine!
I cannot let him win!
What do I do?
What's wrong with
you, Lee?!
[groaning]
You can't lose to this
guy!
You're the real one,
after all!
But, Tenten...! Neji...!
Focus on the bond you
have with your teammates!
That's something the
faker doesn't have!
My bond with Tenten and
Neji. Of course!
[struggling]
I need toilet paper!
Tools, T.P. Summoning
Jutsu!
[gasping]
That enough for the time
being?
Well?
How come when you think
of the bond you have with
us you think of the
bathroom?!
Because when life
caught me with my pants
down, you and Neji both
had my... my backside!
That bond is on thing
thing of mine you
cannot fake!
Tough talk, two-ply!
Fine. Have it your way.
[screaming]
[grunting]
What?!
The?!
Heck?!
"Often Imitated, Never
Duplicated!"
Asakujaku
featuring Rock Lee!
Morning Chicken!
[screaming]
[firing]
[gasping]
Bravo!
Thank you, Tenten!
Too weird, too much!
I couldn't beat the
real Rock Lee. So much
for my dream, I guess.
I'll never be a ninja.
Whaddya mean?
I've wanted to be a
ninja since, like,
forever, but I can't
use ninjutsu at all.
Then one day, I heard
about Rock Lee. He
can't use ninjutsu
either, but he's still
out there giving it his
best shot.
But I didn't have
friends to train with, or
a sensei to guide me, so
it all kinda fell apart.
I got jealous, you
know? Started trollin'
everybody.
All this stems
from that?
I figured I needed
teammates, so I hired
Reji and Zenzen for nine
bucks.
Hey Boss, are you firing
us?
You better
pay me, okay?
There was a time when
I thought being a good
ninja was all about the
external stuff.
Havin' a good team
at your back. That's
the key.
I'm gonna learn from
this and keep trying my
hardest!
Causing trouble in
someone else's name is bad
form, but copying can be
a good way to learn.
Lee's a good guy, so
just do what he would do.
Neither of you can use
ninjutsu, so you're kind
of in the same boat.
You are wrong. Mr.
Impostor has had it
tougher.
Huh?
I have had friends to
help me along the way, but
Mr. Impostor has walked
alone.
In that sense, you
are stronger than I
am, Mr. Impostor.
Aw, Mr. Real
Lee.
Therefore, you can
use my name!
You are not giving away
your name, Lee! Forget
about it!
We're not changing the
title of the show this
far into it!
You can call yourself the
New Rock Lee. I will be
known as Classic Rock
Lee.
Oh no, I just couldn't.
It is fine, really.
Please, no, you're far
too kind.
From one Rock Lee to
another, I insist!
I couldn't possibly
impose like that! Oh, no
no no no!
That's enooough!
[grunting]
That is enough of that,
you violent little girl!
What the--?
[gasping]
Greetings! My name is Pac
Lee! It is true I have no
ninjutsu at my command,
but I can still
defend the weak!
[groaning]
Is this trending
now or something?
Pac Lee is gonna put the
hurt on you four!
[laughing]
Next week's titles are,
"A Hot Night for a
Chilling Tale" and
"The Hokage's Tears
Aren't for Decoration".
A chilling tale, huh?
Actually, ever since the
show started,
I have felt as though
there is someone behind
me. Always watching.
Me, too. It gives me the
creeps.
Maybe there is a ghost
haunting us even now!
He's watching every
move we make with his
dead eyes!!
I am so afraid, Neji!
Um, that's just Yamato
Sensei.