Well folks, here we are in the
middle of autumn. But you know
what?
It's hard to tell that when you
live in the Hidden Sand Village.
See you when I get back.
Be careful.
And say hi to the Leaf
guys for us!
Oh...
Do you have any souvenirs you'd
like me to pick up?
Like what?
If I were picking up something,
it would be one of their
delicacies.
Oh yeah, how 'bought
some saury fish?
That's something we can never
get here in the Sand Village.
Saury?
"We're Here to Welcome Gaara!"
Oh! Gaara is here?
Yes, he arrived earlier today.
We're having a meeting this
afternoon between the two
villages.
He'll be here for a
couple of days.
That is wonderful news!
It has been a while!
Dosukoi! Dosukoi!
I am formally requesting a
match!
Why does it have
to be sumo?!
Very simple. As our bodies
collide in combat, we will
grow closer as friends!
But you aren't colliding,
you're giving him the slip!
And if you watch very carefully,
you'll see you end up pushing
the guy away!
Alright, enough about that.
I want you all to show the
Kazekage our best Leaf
hospitality!
Can I count on you?
[All] Yes!
We need to be hospitable. So
then...
What are you
thinking about?
Actually, sticking with standard
hospitality is our best course.
What does that
mean, exactly?
Here is what I had in mind. I
think pretty much anyone on
earth enjoys a game of Mariko
Kart.
Oh yeah, you're right about
that one! Anyone on earth who
still happens to be in
elementary school!
Can't you come up with something
a little more adult?!
Of course I do not want anyone
to feel left out.
So for people like Satou, who
prefer to read quietly, I will
assemble and provide a good
collection of manga.
I totally know there's always
one guy like that, but who the
heck is Satou?!
Additionally, I plan to have my
mother whip up some snacks that
everyone can enjoy!
Welcome! What can I get
you kids to eat?
Curry!
Oh, give me a break! Everyone
would be terrified of a mom who
looked like that!
Maybe not! I bet Gaara would
find her very interesting!
Now that you mention it, we
don't know if Gaara would be
interested in something
extravagant or uncommon.
And since we don't know, I still
think normal is the best way to
go.
Okay! Let us go buy a game!
Hold it!
Huh?
Guy Sensei?
Lee, I agree that anyone would
have a good time if they
experienced such hospitality.
Right! That is why I
am off to go-
Idiot!
[Grunt]
So why punch him?!
Lee! What was it that Lady
Tsunade said to you?
I want you all to show the
Kazekage our best Leaf
hospitality!
Let me ask you something.
Playing Mariko Kart, reading
manga, eating dinner...
Do you consider that
real hospitality?
Huh.
Let me suggest something.
True hospitality is more like
what I'm about to describe...
I believe it involves
demonstrating your sense of
culture as much as possible...
...so that ultimately, your
guest feels how intelligent and
refined you are.
But you can't feel or sense
anything when your body's going
completely numb!
A true measure of hospitality is
when there is a contest of wills
between the host and the guest.
Those who have experienced such
battles report that they can
feel it in their hearts!
That's because their hearts are
the only places with blood left!
Gaara won't enjoy an activity
that anyone off the street could
do!
You need to use everything
you've cultivated in your
life...
...and hit him with the kind of
hospitality that only you can
provide!
That's the first step to
becoming a true host!
Everything I have cultivated,
and hospitality only I can
provide...
I will do my very best!
But...what is it that I can do
that is unique only to me?
There is my journey to become an
elite ninja, despite my
inability to use ninjutsu...
...but beyond that, I
have no special traits!
You have so many special traits
it's absurd.
You just need a little more
self-awareness.
Right. As I recall, Guy Sensei
said you need to use everything
you've cultivated in your life.
I'd interpret that as drawing on
your experiences, but not trying
to over-achieve.
I see! Experience counts!
I can use the experience points
from the time I spent grinding
away at this one video game...
...trying to finally beat the
last boss!
Have you lost it?! That's for
RPG's not the experience Neji
was talking about!
Well then...
Maybe I can draw from the
feelings I experienced during
those fleeting, bittersweet
summer days...
...I spent with that girl I met
over summer vacation.
Stop it! You don't get to make
up fake summer romances!
It's like your brain downloads
random memories floating around
in space!
I get it. This is not going
very smoothly, is it?
That's because all of your
so-called experience is just
made up.
I bet you could come up with
something that works better, if
you were a little more
realistic.
Realistic?
Of course, I have it!
Huh?
We've now reached that point in
the story where it's time to
entertain Gaara.
It's been awhile.
It has indeed, my friend!
Today, I will show you my own
personal brand of hospitality,
cultivated from all my life's
experience so far!
Great, I look forward to it.
I wonder if this is
really gonna work.
To start, I want you to
race me in Mariko Kart!
Huh?!
You mean after everything we
talked about, the best he could
come up with was that cart
again?!
So without any further delay,
let us begin!
Why are you doing this?!
How can you ask that? I took
your advice and went with
something realistic.
You misunderstood! I
didn't mean real carts!
And this activity isn't
cultivated from your personal
experiences, either!
What in the world do you mean?
Huh?
Think back for a moment, to
all the previous episodes.
All the things we have
experiences in this series. All
the different types of genjutsu!
Like I've said, they're not
genjutsu, they're skits!
Time to race, Gaara!
My hot-blooded passion
will fuel my victory!
He's not kidding about that!
He's flying down the track!
I understand. I don't understand
why we're racing. I guess this
is part of Leaf Hospitality.
You're wrong, Gaara! It's
somebody's interpretation of
hospitality!
[Cheering]
Nice driving, Gaara!
This is a great contest of wills
between the host and the guest!
An example of true hospitality!
The contest was a metaphor, not
to be taken literally!
You're on the right track, Lee!
Now hit Gaara with something
only you can do successfully!
I hear you, Sensei!
Ahh! He literally hit him!
[Groaning]
[Sigh] Well, even with all the
craziness, at least he was
enjoying himself.
Do not worry
yourself, Tenten!
Huh?
I was able to set up a
Satou-style area for just such
an occasion!
You set this up in real-life, as
well?! Neji, have you nothing to
say about this?!
Hey, Lee!
Where's my "Fist of the
Mole" volume four?!
Are you actually sitting
there, reading manga?!
You're right. I have to admit,
it makes no sense. But I
guess this is part of
Leaf hospitality.
Stop accepting everything
at face value!
Attaboy, Lee! What you're doing
here is perfect! It's sure to
make Gaara feel right at home!
Assuming this madness
hasn't numbed his brain!
[Heavy Breathing]
But, now that I think about it,
all that's left for us as hosts,
is to prepare Gaara something
good to eat.
However, that's a tricky task.
You're faced with asking a
private individual like Gaara,
what he'd like to eat.
I'm not sure you'd be able to
trust the information.
You really might be
over-thinking this situation.
Believe me, it is all good!
I will be drawing on my wealth
of experience when it comes to
snack foods!
What am I missing here?
I get it! At dating parties,
it's hard to start a social
conversation.
Having a discussion about your
favorite foods is a great
icebreaker!
Don't you see? It's a smart way
to discover what someone likes
to eat!
I hate to bring up the obvious,
but you could just ask him
directly!
Tell me, why is Gaara
dressed as a girl?
I am utilizing the full depth of
my experience. Notice I am using
Neji in my genjutsu.
I think you're utilizing the
full depth of your stupidity!
Nejie, sweetie, what
can I get you?
You know what? I think I'll
have a bagna cauda!
Here we go again.
And you, Gaako?
Um, well...
Hey, I know! How about some
saury fish? That's something we
can never get here in the Sand
Village.
Saury?
[All] Saury?
All set, Gaara! Here you
go, hope you like it!
[Mmmm]
Delicious!
[Laughing] Success! We did it!
Thank you for today. I really
enjoyed trying out something
new.
Excellent! I am glad we were
able to entertain you!
I agree! For a while, I wasn't
sure what was going to happen!
Ha! I was never the
least bit concerned.
By goofing around together, you
shared a common experience.
Nothing else could have made
that fish taste so good. You
were all emotionally connected.
An excellent job, Lee!
[Heavy Breathing] Guy Sensei!
You're welcome, Lee!
[Crying]
Do you have to carry on like
that in front of us?!
Thanks for
your hospitality!
Another happy ending. But as it
turned out, Gaara took more home
with him than just his pleasant
memories...
That was saury from the
Leaf Village.
You sure?
Going to the Leaf is really
dangerous these days!
No-one could comprehend the
experiences Gaara brought back
from his trip.
Perhaps this is why you can only
get saury in the Leaf?
Autumn is chock full of seasonal
treats to eat! Is anybody else
out there indulging a little too
much?
Excuse me...?
Why in the world are these
pants so tight?
Huh? Can't be...
[Nervous Inhale]
[Loud Scream]
"The Ultimate Autumn Diet!"
You called for me,
Lady Tsunade?
Yes. Glad you're here.
Let's have a talk, regarding
our kunoichi.
Those who have been
practicing in your recent
special training sessions have
found them a bit overwhelming.
I wonder if you could come up
with something more appropriate.
Huh? What do these people mean
by 'overwhelming' specifically?
Well, I get the impression they
mean it's a bit too harsh.
I don't want to tell him it's
his intense personality that's
more overwhelming than anything
else.
I'm sorry...
...But that's how I am! I have
to hold the line!
I absolutely will not change my
methods!
If they can endure my
harsh training regime...
They'll find they can do
remarkable things, like this!
This is exactly what
I'm talking about!
Harsh training doesn't
always work.
Women in particular
sometimes need a little
kindness mixed in.
You want me to train them with
kindness? Really?
Is everybody about
ready to order?
I'm not that hungry. I think
I'll just have an iced tea.
Me too. My stomach
feels kinda full.
I'm not feeling all
that hungry, either.
Me either, when I think about
it. My chest feels full to the
brim already.
[All] Huh?
Really? That doesn't
seem right.
Hmmm.
Mmmm.
Hmph.
So, let me ask. Is everyone
here on a diet?
[Gasps]
So obvious.
Between the sushi, the
matsutake mushrooms, and the
saury, we've had a lot of
food-related episodes lately.
The writers must be hungry or
something all the time.
You think that's
the problem?
What it comes down to is,
everything's so delicious, you
can't help but over-eat!
I have to agree. I, myself, have
gained [Idiot] pounds.
Oh please, you're fine! I
discovered I'm up [Idiot]
pounds!
Well I've gained [Idiot] pounds.
And you, Hinata?
[Idiot] pounds I believe.
[Groans]
This is bad. If the boys found
out, they'd broadcast the news!
This is an emergency! Sakura
Haruno has put on [Idiot]
pounds!
And I can not believe Tenten has
put on [Idiot] pounds!
It's horrifying! We can't let
anybody find out about this!
I promise not to say anything,
even if someone tortures me!
Oh no! They'd never be able to
keep the secret!
You're right! Not a
single one of them!
Especially Naruto!
That settles it. We've gotta
lose this weight, and quick!
But how?
We'll just have to be
intense, brutal even!
Wait a minute, that's it!
Huh?
We just need to apply some of
Guy Sensei's special training!
You're saying that's
the only option?
He's always been a
little too intense.
Remember what Kakashi Sensei
said about Guy's program?
You'd end up burning off a whole
day's calories if you happened
to run into Guy, first thing in
the morning.
What if he's right?
That would be good.
We might even lose
a little extra.
Yeah! Let's try it!
Hmmm.
I'm gonna do it.
Hinata!
Whatever it takes to
lose this weight!
Then I'm in as well!
I wanna slim down!
Alright! I'm on board, too!
Let's take the pledge! We're
gonna burn it off!
[All] We promise to fight 'til
we're right!
Really? You all want
to train with me?
Yes! We talked about it and
decided to come and ask you,
together!
We want the harshest
training you can provide!
Please help us!
What's going on here? I thought
Lady Tsunade said they wanted me
to ease up on the training. Wait
a minute!
[Groaning]
No slacking off! You'll never be
able to beat the boys, if you
have that attitude!
I see. You say he showed no
signs of backing off his harsh
training?
That's very upsetting. I can't
trust our youth to such an
inflexible man.
Might Guy! Negative three
points!
This might be her sneaky way of
evaluating me.
Very well, I'll follow Lady
Tsunade's orders and try to
approach things as she wishes.
I understand! And I'll be
happy to train you!
Sir!
I will lose this flab...
...before the boys know
I put it on!
It's only [Idiot] pounds!
I don't want Naruto
to be grossed out!
Alright! For our first
exercise...
...I'll have you, do a full
ten push-ups!
[All] Are you serious? Ten
push-ups?
Huh?
Is that too many?
What's going on here, Sensei?
Are you making fun of us?
If that was a joke,
we're not laughing!
We wouldn't have come to you if
you weren't going to take us
seriously!
Make the program harsher!
Woah! They're
really into this!
Uhh, okay girls, in that case...
I want you to try and
keep up with me!
They're really doing it!
[Groaning]
That's just stupid!
Next up, try this!
For heaven's sake, why on
earth should we do that?!
Are you telling me you
can't do it?!
No normal person could do that!
[Groaning]
Really?! I guess
you're not normal!
[Heavy Breathing]
[Hmmm]
Harsh training doesn't always
work. Women in particular
sometimes need a little kindness
mixed in.
So she expects a little
kindness from me. I can do that!
Great job, ladies! You've earned
yourself a break! How 'bought a
little treat?
A carrot and stick policy should
work out just right!
What's the matter?
Don't you want it?
No thank you.
Can we just continue on
with the training, please?
Can you give us
something tougher?
[Gasp]
I can't believe it!
Here's the next exercise! Now
try and keep up!
Give me a break! Not the
'Thousand Years of Death!'
[Groaning]
What! You're actually
doing it?
Perhaps they felt too much
pressure to not accept the
carrot part. I understand.
I better ask Lee for help.
[Heavy Breathing]
You are doing great
work girls!
Huh?
We heard you've all been
training pretty hard.
So we brought you
some treats!
[Groaning]
Go ahead, everybody. Dig in!
[Chuckles] I know what they'll
say later.
What? You arranged this
for us, Guy Sensei?
You're so much sweeter than we
thought you were.
How gentlemanly of you!
Yes! An indirect carrot, to go
along with a direct stick
policy!
Look, thanks guys...
...But we just came
here to train.
You really need to
take this stuff away.
What?!
Hold on here! Have I
misunderstood what's going on?
Is it possible they really and
truly want to train under me,
with no ulterior motive?
That aura! It's like they're
burning with passion to achieve
their goals!
This changes everything!
Alright! I'll take them as far
as they want to go!
[Grunting]
You're too slow! Hit it back, no
matter where it comes from!
If you can't handle this,
you'll never be able to
take the gold!
Ahh!
Hinata!
Don't help her!
Stand up, Hinata! Come on, I
know you can do it! Up!
Yes...
Give me another round please.
We're ready for it!
Incredible.
We're just starting.
Follow me, girls!
We're gonna sprint all
the way to the ocean!
Yes!
I'm so happy! They finally
understand my hot-blooded
passion for training!
Well, at least in the short
term...
I am gonna lose this!
I don't understand the point of
any of this.
He's way too intense, but I
can't quit now!
I will get in shape!
[All] We won't quit!
And now for the results...
[Nervous Breathing]
[Groaning]
[Gasps]
I made it!
It was really tough, but it was
worth it!
I set a goal and I achieved it!
I'm so proud of myself, really!
[Laughing]
You should all be
proud of yourselves.
You survived my toughest
training.
Right now I can't help myself,
I'm bursting with joy!
Guy Sensei!
[Crying] You're some of the best
students I've ever had!
Congratulate yourselves on a
job well done!
Time for a reward!
Huh?
Everyone, eat up!
After all you went through,
it's my treat!
[Gasps]
This is good! Mmmm delicious!
Thank you Sensei! It was very
generous of you to let us all
join in!
You should have
some of this, Hinata!
The hunger meter's
approaching max! It may blow!
Batten the hatches
on the port side!
The third line's
been breached!
We're in trouble! The fourth
line can't bear the pressure!
[Screams]
It's over! We can't hold out
anymore!
Bear down! We just have to get
through this meal!
[Screams]
[Eating Loudly]
And so, they instantly
rebounded. And the ultimate
autumn diet ended in failure.
Apparently, Guy Sensei will
never understand the hearts of
young women.
Tune in for our next episodes,
which will be:
"Autumn Shinobi Safety Lessons,"
and "Deidara's Art is Always a
Blast!"
Let's proceed with youthful
energy!
I'm done with youthful energy!
I'll just rebound again. And
explosions are dangerous! We'll
just get hurt!
I think a blast is just what
we need to shake things up!
Whaddya say, let's blast them
wi
th the flames of our youth!
The truth is, it doesn't matter
what you say...
There's no way to control it!
Guy Sensei's mind is always
exploding with something!