(Sakura)
It should be ready!
(Naruto)
Finally..!
It's time to
chow down!
[freaking out]
Hot! Hot! Hot!
You have to let it
cool down for a
little bit first,
you idiot!
Alright, only one
thing to do...
Rasengan Mini!
There! Now that
oughta take care
of it! [slurps]
"The No-Ninjutsu Lifestyle"
Hmm, it seems like
lately they've been
using ninjutsu a lot...
...but only for
the most trivial
reasons...
[groan] What should
I do about it?
(Guy)
What should I do about it?
Huh?
(Kakashi)
Guy..?
That's the question...
What to do...
Is something
wrong, Guy?
No, it's really
nothing. Nothing
to worry about
at all!
If that's the vase,
then please... go
and wash the curry
off your face!
Huh?!
Well, actually,
Lee...
[gasp] Oh no! This
curry is going to
leave a hard-to-remove
stain!
Ahhh! Great Leaf
Hurricane!!!
I didn't give him all
of that training so he
could use his moves
inappropriately like that.
Seriously, just
clean your face.
Although, I have to
admit, Lee's hard
work is paying off!
Lately his moves are
looking as sharp as
a knife with another
knife taped to it.
Guy, for real.
Your face is
covered in curry.
But still! It's the
principle of the matter!
I feel as though
he's merely taking
his abilities for
granted...
He's out there using his
strength as a ninja for the
most trivial tasks instead
of for important deeds!
The words of an old
man who reeks of
curry don't carry
much weight...
Did you just say
I've got old man
stink!?!
Enough already,
Guy!!!
Uh, [clears throat]
I can sympathize. I
was just thinking
the same thing.
You were?
Seriously?
I'd like to find a way to
teach out pupils to have a
little more appreciation
for their ninja skills.
Well, we're just
going to have to
be blunt with them.
Convince them they
can't become elite
shinobi or Hokage
that way!
But they're not
kids anymore.
It's gonna take more
than a pep talk to hook
them in and get them to
change their ways...
Hook them in..?
That's brilliant!
It just might work!
What..?
Just leave everything
to me! They'll fall
for this plan, hook,
line, and sinker!
[birds chirping]
Idiot. Idiot.
(Kids)
Real world
experience?
Just think of it as
a social studies class.
It sounds
interesting!
I cannot wait!
Yeah, but, why us?
What are we supposed
to be learning?
I don't see Guy
Sensei anywhere
either...
Well, he...uh,
Guy had something come
up, so he asked me to
chaperone all of you.
Okay. Where are
we going, anyway?
Ummm...
We'll make them all
do hard labor, without
letting them use any
of their ninjutsu!
And the absence of
their special powers
will make them appreciate
their gifts even more...
You think they'll
bite? I mean,
those guys...?
Oh they'll bite
alright! Because
they'll be fishing!
Fishing...?
We're going to spend the
day on a fishing boat!
In my experience, exper
-iancing a little honest,
hard work is an excellent
learning experience.
Are you kidding me?
This is such a drag.
Now don't be
like that...
Uh, Sensei? Can we
bring a few bananas
for snack time?
Yeah, Sensei! And a
cup of ramen for lunch?
And locally-sourced
delicacies for my rice?
Ia food all you
guys think about?
Guy said to leave
everything to him...
But I wonder if he'll
actually show up.
Huh?
Oh, boy, don't
tell me...
Ahh... So
you're here!
It's Guy alright.
This is ridiculous!
They'll see right
through that disguise!
Hey, what exactly is
is going on here,
Kakashi Sensei?
I can tell that he
is no fisherman.
I mean, come on!
It's so obvious,
even to us!
[weary sigh]
I knew it.
With that hair,
he surely must
be an ex baseball
player!
That hair means
he's a boxer!
Ding ding ding!
Ya know?
Technically, that's
a fro. With hair like
that, he must be a famous
Japanese ballad singer.
Can we have
your autograph!?
Oh come on! Don't
ask him that!
Thank goodness,
they can't tell...
Thank you so much
for having us onboard
your ship!
Just one thing
before we set
sail...
While you're on
board my ship, none
of you are allowed
to use ninjutsu!
(Thinking)
Perfect... if
this works...
Boy... this really
is very difficult.
I haven't even
gotten a nibble
today...
This is just
impossible
without ninjutsu!
You see? Now do you
understand just how
lucky you are to be
able to use it at all?
From now on, make
sure you use ninjutsu
more responsibly!
Oh, Kakashi Sensei!
[pleased chuckle]
This is ridiculous!
Why aren't we allowed
to use ninjutsu?
Yeah! This
isn't fair!
Well, you see...
(Disguised Guy)
That's enough!
Huh??
I'll tell you
all why!
It happened back
when I was only
sixteen years old...
What!?
(Disguised Guy)
I was a juvenile delinquent
with a bit of a reputation
in this harbor town...
Wassap!?
What kind of origin
story is this!? And
who is that!?
(Disguised Guy)
Back then, 'bout all I thought
was "I wanna get out of this
one-boat hole of a town..."
(Disguised Guy)
But my dad had other ideas.
He wanted me to take over
the family business...
(Disguised Guy)
So we had a big
fight, and I ran
away...
(Kakashi)
Guy, er, fisherguy. We don't
need to know what happened
before you left!
(Disguised Guy)
Flash forward to five
years later...
(Disguised Guy)
It's Spring, and I've made
my home in the capital.
(Disguised Guy)
But I was living paycheck
to paycheck with no real
direction in life...
(Disguised Guy)
Then one night, I ate the most
delicious boiled squid I'd ever
had, and it made me homesick.
(Disguised Guy)
Then I noticed that everyone
else was eating the same thing,
and they all looked so happy.
(Disguised Guy)
Then I understood...
I thought he was just a two-bit
fisherman, but my dad... he was
accomplishing something big.
(Disguised Guy)
Making so many people
happy by catching
those fish...
(Disguised Guy)
By the time I made it back
to my hometown, my dad was
ill and on his deathbed.
(Disguised Guy)
Ever since, I've been on this
boat, catching fish and doing
something good with my life...
I'm bringing joy to
others, just like my
dear old dad did!
That had nothing to do
with ninja at all!
What happened to
explaining why they
can't use ninjutsu?
[crying]
That was such a
beautiful story!
Huh?!
Yeah, sure was!
You're a great man!
I'm gonna start
bawling!
Tryin' to be such
a strong guy can
be such a drag...
That boiled squid
sounded so tasty...
I think I speak for everyone
when I say we will respect
your wishes and refrain
from using our ninjutsu!
-Yeah...
Wait... what!?
Am I supposed to
do the punch-
lines today?
This boat's
so rocky!
Are we gonna be
okay if we can't
use our ninjutsu
at all?
Of course! This is
the perfect opportunity
to learn the physical
limits of your bodies.
Remember, this fisherman
does his job every day
without any ninjutsu.
Indeed!
Huh?
Now... the first thing
to get used to is, the
movement of the boat.
Why don't you
get used to it
first??
Everything's okay.
I can handle it.
Alright, folks.
Let's catch some
fish!
The bait's
over there...
Huh?
What!? Are you
insane!? That's
the bait you're
eating!!
I'm hungry! Besides,
it's good enough
for the fish!
Yes, I hear
you. How tasty!
Being on a boat
works up an appetite!
This isn't
bad at all!
What!? Seriously!?
Not you guys too!
Hey! All of you
guys stop fooling
around on my boat!
Maybe they would if
you hadn't set such
a bad example!
Oh, hee hee!
Don't "hee hee" me!
We don't have
any more bait
to fish!
Never fear!
Huh?
[shouts]
We've got
bait costumes!
What good will
it do us if
you're the bait!?
Ah ha! So we still
have that option!
[groan]
But what could we
possibly catch
with those things!?
(Lee)
I was thinking we would land
some of those fangirls that are
into guys who look kinda tough!
He does make a good point.
Girls these days are really
into that kind of look.
Exactly! Girls of
every generation like
a guy who's not afraid
to show some skin!
Isn't that,
right Sakura!?
Uhhh...
Actually, I think what
girls truly prefer is a
guy who has muscles!
Correct, Sakura?
Not that again!
You're wrong!
Women prefer a
man in medieval
underwear!
No! No one
prefers that!
Alright! We caught
a ton of fish!
It's so much easier
with ninjutsu. It's
really the only
way to go!
I know! Besides,
we had no other
choice! We didn't
have any bait left!
[sigh] I guess
it's hopeless.
Huh?
Huh!? What's that!?
[screams]
No way! What is
that huge thing?
Giant boiled squid!
No, it's stuffed squid!
It is ink-redible
dried squid!
You're all completely wrong!
Can't you guys ever think
about anything besides food!?
[screams]
[shouting]
We gotta calm
that thing down!
But the boat's rocking
too much for us to use
ninjutsu against it!
This trip is turning
into a real drag.
We're just gonna have
to give that thing a
good pounding then!
Right! Count me in!
I guess we have
no choice...
(Disguised Guy)
Wait!
I told you, no one
is going to use
ninjutsu while they're
on board my ship!
Guy Sensei!?
Now, watch
closely.
Yooowww!!!
Hiiieeeyya!
He's nuts!
Shrimp Tossing High
Jump Tornado Punch!
[stunned awe]
Guy Sensei!
Guy..?
Hiiiyaaahh!
Woooah!
Guy Sensei!
What are
all of you!?
Huh?
You're ninja! You
shouldn't abuse your
powers to accomplish
trivial tasks!
[gasps]
To be truly strong shinobi,
you must only use your
abilities to achieve big
important accomplishments!
You understand?!
[gasp] Yes!
Now... Hot!!!
We're gonna have
to find a way to
cool this off.
I guess so. It
looks like we're
back to square one.
Sakura, we are not.
Ninja must never
use their powers for
small insignificant
things!
Instead we must only
use out incredible
abilities for big,
important tasks!
Yeah! You got
that right, Lee!
You know this
isn't what he
meant by "big,"
right?
(Narrator)
And so, Naruto and Lee aim to
achieve bigger and better things
using their ninja abilities.
(Narrator)
Of course, bigger
isn't always better.
Well, I guess
that's not such
a bad ending.
Oh!
Hi Sakura!
Huh? Oh! Lee!
Waiting for
the rain to stop?
Hah, yeah,
unfortunately.
Wait, you don't
have an umbrella
either?
This is just
another form
of training!
Oh, I see.
Huh?
[humming]
Hey, Naruto! Let me
share your umbrella!
Well, see ya later,
Lee!
Oh...
Thanks, I really
appreciate this!
No problem! Anything
for you! C'mon, I'll
walk you home.
(Sakura)
[giggle]
"I Want to Share an
Umbrella With Sakura"
Huh?
Is something
wrong, Tenten?
Is that... Lee?
Hmm... I cannot
decide whether I
like that pattern
better...
What do you
mean, Lee?
I mean the umbrella
in back that has the
floral print...
[screams]
Please do not
scare me like that!
I'm the one who
should be saying
that to you!
Lee, what are you
up to, anyway?
I uh... Well,
I... Um...
What's going on?
You're acting really
weird right now.
[sigh]
Hm?
(Tenten)
Oh... I see.
You're upset because
you missed a chance
to get close to Sakura
under an umbrella, right?
I wouldn't worry if
you didn't have an
umbrella this time
and missed a chance.
It's the rainy
season, after all. You
should have plenty
more opportunities.
That's not the problem,
Guy Sensei gave Lee an
assignment a while ago...
Listen, Lee, you never
can tell when it might
suddenly become rainy
or windy during battle.
So to prepare yourself
to deal with adverse
weather, I want you not
to use an umbrella!
Yes! I understand,
Guy Sensei!
La la la la!!
Remember, going out
without an umbrella
will be training, Lee!
Let's roll!
Right!
Laa la la la la!
Oh give me a break!
Forget training, you
guys are just goofing
off in the rain!
I could never just
ignore a training
mission from Guy
Sensei...
But still... I
want to...
...I want to smuggle
with Sakura under an
umbrella!
Wait, did you just
say, "smuggle?" It's
"snuggle," numbskull!
Listen, if you're
that upset, why not
just go talk to Guy
Sensei?
I bet if you asked
he'd let the umbrella
thing slide,
Do you think so?
Well it couldn't be
thatimportant, he
didn't tell us not to
carry them after all...
And besides, Guy
Sensei isn't some
heartless ogre.
Oh, yes! You
are right!
(Guy Sensei)
You fool!
[crying in pain]
[gasps]
If you were merely some
ordinary ninja, then I'd
have no problem at all with
you carrying an umbrella.
(Guy)
But Lee... You cannot use
ninjutsu. If you want to
become an elite ninja...
...ordinary every day
activities must become
training!
And if you aren't
able to understand
that, then you're
hopeless!!
I am sorry...!
(Tenten)
Look how sad
he is...
We really messed
this one up, don't
you think?
If you ask me, Guy
Sensei's being too
strict about this
whole thing...
I mean training is
important, but...
That's it! It's
training!
Training?
Yeah! If we can turn carrying an
umbrella into training somehow,
Guy Sensei shouldn't have any
objections to you using one!
It makes sense!
So c'mon! Cheer
up, okay?
We'll start using
umbrella training
right away!
And I suppose I'll
help out, too!
Congratulations!
Nice umbrella!
Not like that!!
Tenten, this is the
only kind of umbrella
related training that
I could think of!
Look, this isn't
a broadway show!
You're not even the
one who's using the
umbrella, Lee!
Then...
Cha-- Shu--!!!
No golfing on the
train platform!!
Now get serious,
would you?
I really was
being serious!
But try as I might,
I just cannot think
of a good way to train
with an umbrella!
Okay fine, I'll
help out....
Wait, how 'bout
we try...
Whew! A weighted
umbrella!
Just holding this massive
thing is training, no
matter how you slice it!
No no no no!
That is easy
for you to
say, Tenten!
But this is
impossible!
Look! Just quit your
griping and pick it
up already!
[weeping]
[groaning]
So... heavy!!
Neji... catch!
Why!? Why is it
always me!?
[groaning]
This one is...
far too heavy!
Stop your
whining!
Hard work's supposed
to be your trademark,
isn't it!?
Oh, that is right!
Hard work is my
trademark!
I understand now!
I will do my best!
Well it appears that
he's finally back to
normal.
Mhm!
(Narrator)
And so, the three teammates
embarked upon a harsh
training regimen...
Hey! Steady!
You're wobbling!
If you can't walk
straight then Sakura
will get soaked!
Right!
Come on, come on!
Just be glad those
weights aren't any
heavier!
Again! Lift it up!
[grunting]
Just two more
reps after you
reach the top!
[groans]
Nice! You've really
gotten pretty good
at holding that one
up, Lee!
No more, catch!
Ow! But why!?
Why always me!?
[straining]
Sakura, would you
like to take a
walk with me?
That voice... Lee?
[screaming]
Heavy! Ugh!
You can't ask her
with that look on
your face!!
You could just tell me
that instead of
smashing me...
You know, Tenten,
I think you're
overdoing things
a bit...
Grrr!
Alright, fine. I'll
handle things from
here on out!
[jumbled speech]
Sakura, would you
like to take a
walk with me?
That voice... Lee?
[screaming]
Eight Trigrams!
Sixty Four Palm!
And you call that
handling it!?
(Lee)
Sakura! Get under
my umbrella!
(Tenten)
More polite!
(Lee)
Walk in my umbrella!
(Neji)
Too pushy,
weird grammar!
(Lee)
Shall we go into
my umbrella?
(Tenten)
Seriously bad grammar!
[panting]
You did it!
Yes! You're holding
that heavy umbrella
in the air like it's
nothing at all!
And your invitation
to Sakura is really
smooth now!
Uh, Lee? What's
the matter?
Well... Neji...
Tenten...
Thank you so much!
I really appreciate
you doing all this
for me!
Lee...
Are you crying?
No way! I simply have
a little mucus coming
out of my eyes right now!
You could have
just said it was
sweat, ya know.
Pretend I did!
Listen, you'd better not
look this pathetic when
you approach Sakura tomorrow!
I will not!
I will do
my best!
(All)
[chuckling]
(Villager)
Man! When the rainy
season ends, it sure
ends quickly, doesn't it!?
(Villager)
Thank goodness for
that high pressure front!
(Villager)
Let's go to the beach!
[sad sigh]
(Tenten)
Excuse me...
Huh?
Well, Lee, can
we all share
your umbrella?
The sun's very strong
today, we could all
use a little shade!
[happy sigh]
If you insist,
than, sure!
[giggle]
This is not a three
person umbrella,
thought, so it is
a bit cramped...
No complaining now!
(Lee)
It was summer, many
years ago...
(Lee)
I wanted to become a
ninja, even though I
cannot use ninjutsu.
(Lee)
And Guy Sensei took me
under his wing without
a second thought!
(Lee)
Now, Guy Sensei, the
time has come for me
to surpass you!
(Lee)
The next time on Rock
Lee and His Ninja Pals...
(Lee)
I will surpass
Guy Sensei!
(Lee)
I will beat you,
Guy Sensei, just
you wait!