(Narrator)
A long, bitter winter has
everyone in the village
feeling down...
(Narrator)
But no one feels
downer than--
(Shizune)
Lady Tsunade...
Please! You must
snap out of it!
Something the matter?
Take a look!
Guuuh!!
[groans]
What is it that
ails you, M'lady!?
This miserable weather.
It happens
every winter!
Day after day, being
cooped up inside, with
nothing to think about
except how broke I am...
...and how I've done
nothing with my life
but collect gambling
debts...
...and how long it
is 'til payday.
...I tell you, it
makes my heart
very cold and heavy.
As our Hokage, your
mood directly affects
the morale of the
village!
We can do noting about the
weather or your gambling
debts, however we'll soon
find a way to warm your heart!
Yeah... good luck
that that...
[groans]
Wait! I have it!
"A Fiery Snow-Sculpting Contest"
Lady Tsunade herself will
be choosing the winner,
so give it all you've got!
Let's see which one of
you can make a snow
sculpture that will warm
our beloved Hokage's heart!
Yeah yeah, okay,
your beloved Hokage
is freezing her
beloved buns off!
So come on! Let's
get on with it!
[shivering]
(Lee)
This is hopeless! Just look
at her cold indifference!
Nothing we do can fix that!
Yeah, that look she just
gave us lowered the
temperature ten degrees!
Trying to warm her
heart is going to be
an impossible mission.
Mission!? What mission!?
This isn't even a mission!
Well! It would appear you
all need some motivation!
Then I will have to come up
with a prize for the winner
that will really light a
fire under your posteriors!
Like what? A half-
price coupon for a
bowl-cut?
Even better!
Whoever makes the best
ice sculpture will win...
...a kiss...
Huh?
Exactly! The winner of the
contest will earn the right
to give a big kiss to whoever
he or she has a crush on!
Yes, for one lucky shinobi,
Valentines Day is going to
come a little early this year!
And if that doesn't li
ght a--
That's ridiculous!
Nobody's gonna--
I will win this contest
and earn the right to
kiss Sakura, even at
the cost of my life!
Sorry, Bushy Brow!
But if anyone's
kissing Sakura, I am!
That really worked
on you guys? I
don't believe it!!
I've got to win to
make sure neither
thing happens!
To kiss Naruto...
[sigh]
Don't even think
of it, Hinata!
Alright! Who's
ready to bring it
on and win it all?
Meee!
No!
And who wants
to win that kiss!?
Meeee!
Nooo!
So let the
battle begin!
Wow! They're already
going at it!
So, this is where
I belong. Right
here with these
guys... huh.
[groan]
For some reason, it
feels colder here
than out there...
[nervous laugh]
With their hearts and minds
a frenzy of emotions, the
competitors go at it!
Each trying to
out-do the other!
Huh?
[smooching sounds]
(Shizune)
What in the world
are Lee and Naruto
doing?
Obviously they're
practicing their
kissing!
How gross it that!?
That's right! Use
that youthful passion!
Not in a million years!
(Sakura)
No way I'm gonna
let one of them win!
All done!
My sculpture is called,
"You guys are out of your
minds if you think I'm
going to let you kiss me!"
Sakura's sculpture
gives me shivers!
You can almost feel the
rage inside of her building
to one of her trademark
monster punches!
What do you think,
Lady Tsunade?
That's just what she
wants to happen...
[gasp]
A fine effort and a bold
artistic statement, but
I'm afraid it didn't
resonate with Lady Tsunade,
SO YOU LOSE!
AhhhH!
Finished! I call it...
Summertime!
Doesn't it make you think
of sun and sweat, and the
sun pouring down on your head?
Wow, it's straightforward.
Lady Tsunade?
He's just begging
for attention...
[gasp]
Reminding her of
heat just amplified
the cold.
YOU LOSE TOO.
Guhh, rats!
[groan]
Wait! Don't give
up hope yet! It
looks like Hinata's
finished...
What could it
be, I wonder...
Well I feel that if you really
want to touch a person &amp; warm
their heart, the first thing you
do is try to understand them.
That's deep.
Huh. She's got
a point...
Whatever, I think we all
know who this is going
to be a sculpture of..
(Thinking)
I've always been
watching you...
Wishing I could get
closer to you...
Closer....
Closer..!
Wanting to get
to know you!
Huh?
[embarrassed squeal]
What the--!? I
thought for sure
you'd make a
statue of Naruto!
Oh I couldn't
possibly..!
But this old man
reminds me of a special
day, and the way Naruto
looked standing there...
That doesn't even
make sense!!
[whimper]
A good concept spoiled
in the execution by
your terminal shyness...
ANOTHER LOSER!
But I'll always
have the memories...
Enough of this! I'm colder
than ever! In fact, I'm
starting to lose the feeling
in my toes!
Wait M'lady! We
are not done..!
Yeah! You haven't
seen our sculptures
yet!
Okay, I really don't see
the point in continuing
this any longer...
But.. M'lady!
Alright! This
contest is over!
-No way!!!
Are you giving up!?
What else can we
do, Guy Sensei?
[groan]
I feel sorry for
Lady Tsunade...
She's reaping what
she has sown...
A shinobi gains wisdom
from the mistakes he
has made...
Is there nothing you
can learn from your
failure and the others?
Let me see...
I'll try...
That's just what she
wants to happen...
He's just begging
for attention...
I feel that if you really want
to touch a person and warm their
heart, the first thing you must
do is try to understand them.
Huh. She's got
a point...
Hang on!
I've got it!
Naruto..?
I'll have granny
Tsunade warmed up
in no time!
(Tsunade)
Huh!?
Why the hell am I
still wearing this?!
[knock knock knock]
[gasp]
Narubei, what's wrong?
My poor brother...
Something's wrong
with him!
(Tsunade)
This is serious...
He looks so pale...
Actually, that's pretty
much how Sai always looks.
Please! You have
to save him!
We're only a small
village clinic...
This is out of my
league...
Oh, don't say that,
Doc! There's nobody
else I can turn to,
NOBODY!
Please! You gotta
save him! I'm
begging you!
He's the only family
I have left in the
whole wide world!!!
Very well..
I'll do everything
I can !
Bravo!
Wait, what's
going on?
Behold! The powerful
urge to heal a
patient in need!
Naruto's
long relationship
with Lady Tsunade is
paying off!
He knows just how
to push her medical
jutsu buttons!
Is this still part of
the snow sculpture
contest..?
So that is his
game! Well two
can play at
that, Naruto!
Narubei, is Saijirou
going to be all right?
And you are?
And old friend of
the family's...
I have a little
medical training
myself...
...let me
assist you...
Dear me! This
is awful!
-Why!? What is it!?
This calls for a
very difficult
operation...
But it must be
done, or he will
not last the night.
Oh no! Nooo!
If we succeed, he will
make a full recovery...
But the odds are
fifty-fifty, at best.
The.. odds!?
That is right. This
operation is a gamble.
And I hear you are
not very lucky when
it comes to gambling.
That's not true!!
I always beat the
odds when lives are
at stake!
That'shis angle..!
Okay, I'll bite.
What's his angle?
A frontal attack on
her greatest weakness!
As soon as he said
what the odds were,
he ignited the gambling
demon that lies within!
What a clever move!
Lee knows Lady Tsunade
can never resist a bet.
Talk about pushing buttons!
So, we're just forgetting
all about the snow sculpting?
Heh heh! Nice one.
I can't believe I
fell for that!
Ha ha ha!
(Guy)
So, feeling a bit
warmer, are we?
Yep! I won't use the
weather as an excuse
to mope around any more.
Besides, I've no right
to be depressed..!
Not when I have so many
wonderful people worrying
about my well-being.
(Tenten)
You're so right,
Lady Tsunade!
(Neji)
It's certainly a relief
to see you back to your
old self again!
Wait a minute!!! Are
we to forget about
the contest!?
Yeah! Who won,
me, or Bushy Brow?
Oh, who cares? I
feel better now,
that's all that
matters...
Wait! Their manly
desires must be
fulfilled!
Go on! Appeal to
their Hokage for
a decision!
C'mon, granny!
I won and you
know it!
No, I won! Did I
not, Lady Tsunade?
Get outta here, Lee!
You get outta here!
All right, you two,
stop this at once--
AHHHHH!
[screaming]
[gasps]
You two are about to be
very sorry you did that!!
(Narrator)
Her energy restored, Lady
Tsunade made her own snow
sculpture...
(Narrator)
...which she called "The
Punishment for Goofing
Around."
Don't, M'lady!
What? My wallet's full
again and I'm feeling
lucky...
But what if you
lose again!?
You'll never hit a home
run if you don't step
up to the plate!
And I'm gonna win it
all back! Plus interest!
(Narrator)
Proving the old gamblers adage,
if at first you don't succeed,
try try again. And again.
Not much of a turn out,
but it's the best we
could do on such short
notice.
It's not bad, considering
Kakashi Sensei's call for
a joint training exercise
came out of nowhere.
[sigh] I just wish
it was a real mission.
Look, we're here because
Kakashi Sensei asked us.
Training's good
once in a while.
(Narrator)
On the surface, everything
seems perfectly normal with
Lee and his friends...
(Narrator)
But underneath, they're
anything but calm, Why?
(Narrator)
Because today is
Valentine's Day!
"The Battlefield Called
Valentine's Day"
(Thinking)
They say Valentine's Day is a
special day when boys get choc-
olates from girls who like them
...But I have never
gotten so much as a
chocolate chip!
That is because, every year,
and the year before, in fact,
everyyear, I have been out
on a mission with Guy Sensei!
...or out training
with Guy Sensei..!
...or out eating curry
with Guy Sensei...!
[cries]
Forget chocolate! I
have never even seen a
girl on Valentine's Day!
(Thinking)
Yeah, same here! Every year
when Valentine's Day rolls
around I've been off...
Training with Pervy Sage!
If you can call it training...
Mostly it means dragging his
drunk butt home from some
girly joint. Every year I've
missed out on chocolate!
Well this year's
gonna be different!
[girly giggles]
[determined grunts]
(Thinking)
My rivals are after
the chocolate, too!
I must strike first!
[girly giggles]
Hello, girls! Do
you have any choc--
What are you doing!?
You'd better read
this before you
blow it,
(Lee)
"The Boys Guide to
Valentine's Day"..?
"Rule number one: Don't
make it obvious that
you want chocolate...
...or the girls will
most likely ignore
you completely!"
...and not even give
you a pity piece!"
"Worst case scenario,
they'll go and give your
share of chocolate to
their friends!"
Chocolate! Chocolate!
Ugh! I'm not
giving you any!
Here Ino! From one
friend, to another.
Thanks, Sakura!
-Nooooooooo!
My Byakugan tells me
that the girls definitely
have... chocolate in
their shopping bags.
That was close. I almost
lost the battle before
it had even begun.
This is it! The year
when we finally score
some valentines!
[girly giggles]
(Thinking)
The problem is, the girls
just seem to be ignoring
us anyway...
I am beginning to
suspect they have
forgotten what day
this is..!
(Thinking)
Maybe the training
exercise has made
them distracted!
What do we
do now?
(Naruto)
Hey! Remember christmas
and New Years? They sure
were a blast, weren't they?
Ah! Good strategy!
Yes, a very clever move
trying to jog their memory
by reminding them of
recent holidays...
Let us provide
backup!
There is nothing like
a holiday to bring
people together!
We all had
such a great time!
Yeah! Christmas was
great! Can't wait
'til next year!
[giggle]
[anxious breaths]
Anyway..!
[girly giggles]
Nothing! They
didn't even flinch!
I guess we underestimated
just how dense they are!
Perhaps we just
confused them by
dragging Christmas
into it..!
New Plan...!
I am feeling faint.
It must be low
blood sugar...
Oh! I get it!
He's going to trick
them into giving him
chocolate for medicinal
purposes!
Not bad, Bushy Brow!
Ooo... Feeling
faint..!
Didn't get enough
to eat today...
[groans]
I can't believe you!
Don't tell me you guys
skipped breakfast!
-Huh?
It's the most important
meal of the day! The
key to building up your
energy reserves!
Without proper nutrition, the
right balance of carbs, fats, &amp;
proteins, how can you expect to
complete a dangerous mission?
(Sakura)
You'll be jeopardizing
your teammates' health
as well as your own!
(Thinking)
What happened!? Instead
of chocolate, we're getting
a lecture on nutrition!
(Thinking)
Sakura can go on like this all
day. Next she'll tell us about
fiber and micronutrient rations
What's really good are
whole grains! The best
way to start the day!
I love green juice
and soy milk!
They say burdock
tea is very good
for you.
Green juice and soy
milk are way better
than that stuff.
I feel as if I were
trapped in the health
segment of a morning
talk show...!
Soy Milk? We've gotten
way off topic...
Guess this wasn't such
a great idea after all.
But then how do
we get them back
on topic?
And fast! We've gotta think
of a way to get the topic back
on chocolate before Kakashi
Sensei gets here!
I'm hungry. Is
anybody else hungry?
[gasps]
Of course!!
[drooling]
(Thinking)
Only Choji could
get away with a
move like that!
(Thinking)
Yeah, when your stomach's
a bottomless pit like his,
you can always act hungry!
...without arousing
suspicion, no matter
how big a breakfast
you've had...
(Thinking)
Could that be his
strategy..?
You girls have
any snacks on you?
Sure! You want
some chocolate?
(Lee)
So simple, and yet,
so brilliant!
[chomp]
(Thinking)
Genius move, Choji!
I'm starting to see
you in a whole new light!
[grunt]
-Go, Choji, go!
Anyone mind if I
eat lunch early?
[nom nom nom]
[screaming]
We'll just exchange
friendship chocolate!
Noooooooo!
I give up!
This beating around
the bush is getting
us nowhere!
If only we could just
come out and say the
word "chocolate"..!
(Thinking)
I wish someone would say it!
I've been so looking forward
to Valentine's Day...
...but it's hard
to break the ice!
...if only someone
would just ask...
Chocolate? Why, yes!
I have some right here!
(thinking)
Then I could give my
chocolate away without
seeming pushy!
(Thinking)
Wait... I wonder
if Hinata...
Yes..! I suspect she is
dying to give away her
chocolate, but she is held
back by that absurd shyness!
If I can get past that,
she could be the thin
edge of the wedge!
And if Hinata falls,
the rest will follow,
like dominos..!
I just need to
create the right
opportunity..!
LIsten, everyone!
Instead of juts standing around
doing nothing, why don't we use
this time to stimulate a
dangerous mission scenario!?
Like... for example,
being lost in the
mountains in a blizzard!
Look! Is that a
cabin over there?
[groan]
Oh, Lee! Are
you alright?
Yes, but alas, I lost
the backpack with our
supplies!
We will have to break
into the emergency rations!
Yes, we will! I'll
pass them out.
Here's your
emergency ration.
Huh? What on
earth is that?
A jawbreaker!
[screaming]
What are you
thinking?!
Maintaining our stamina in high-
altitude, sub-zero temperatures
will require us to eat something
far more substantial than that!
Are you mad?!
Excuse me, but I believe
jawbreakers are the
standard emergency ration.
What's the big
idea, Neji!?
Who's side is
he on!?
He betrayed us!
I want chocolate as much
as anyone! But I happen to
know that Hinata made those
with her own hands!
She put her heart
and soul into them!
Kinda looks like
rabbit poop.
I'm afraid you'll say
something stupid like
that and break her heart!
I will protect my cousin
form harm, no matter what!
(Thinking)
I don't understand
what's going on, Neji!
Don't stand in
our way..!
We will take
them by force!
Just try it...!
What tasty treat
starts with the
letter "c"?
Cantaloupe!
What is brown
and sweet?
Coffee with sugar!
[panting]
What did the Aztecs
think their gods ate?
Ooooof!
I don't speak Aztec.
his defenses are
unstoppable!
[groan] We must
keep trying!
What do you drink...
piping hot with marsh-
mellows in it?
You are choc full
of stupid!
[echo]
Choc full of stupid!
...full of choc!
...full of chocolate!
Heh heh heh!!!
Yes! Victory!
We did it! We
finally got someone
to say the word!
It wasn't easy! We stumbled, we
made mistakes, we got knocked
down, we were betrayed, but we
hung in there and we did it!
Try not to get
too emotional...
we still have not--
(Kakashi)
Sorry I'm late...
...but you wouldn't believe
how many people kept stopping
me to give me these...
Kakashi Sensei...
are those---?
Yep. And I got way
more than I could ever
eat. You guys want some?
-Noooooooooooo!
(Narrator)
So, Rock Lee and the
boys missed out again--
(Narrator)
--as the girls were just
waiting to give Kakashi Sensei
their sought after gifts.
(Narrator)
But the boys did get their
friendship chocolates...!
Better luck next time!
(Tenten)
Next time: "The Legendary Sanin
Jiraya" and "Infiltrates the
Women's Bath!"
(Tenten)
Wait a second, why is
Pervy Sage showing up
again?
(Lee)
To fill a need,
I believe.
(Lee)
Viewers seems to think
this anime is lacking
in sex appeal.
(Tenten)
Really? People want
moreof that?
(Lee)
Yes indeed! I have sent
in a few requests myself!
(Naruto)
Yeah, me too!
(Kakashi)
I send the producers a
crate a week, sometimes two!
(tenten)
You, too, Kakashi Sensei?!
(Tenten)
Man, I swear you
men are all alike!