Matsutake mushroom rice,
steamed matsutake mushrooms,
grilled matsutake mushrooms,
matsutake mushroom tempura!
Ah, autumn! Such a
fragrant and tasty
season!
Oh, autumn! Autumn!
Finally, a matsutake
mushroom hunt!
It's been so long.
Guy Sensei and
Kakashi Sensei are
both on cloud nine.
Of course! We are here to
pick matsutake mushrooms!
Hunt, hunt, hunt!
[screaming]
Stop, Lee! Do you
have something
against me? Stop!
Lee's got the right
spirit but entirely
the wrong place.
Huh? Weird, what
was that?
"Hunting for Matsutake
Mushrooms!"
There aren't any
mushrooms anywhere!
I don't understand
it! Where did they
all go!
And we came all this
way to gather them.
Well, unfortunately, we
had an unusually hot
summer. So we didn't have
the conditions we need
for them to grow well.
As you see, this is the
only one we've found after
looking for the whole day.
Full course!
Time to eat!
Nom nom, slurp,
huff and puff, burp!
Even the local restaurants
have had to get the supplies
for their matsutake mushroom
dishes imported from grocery
stores outside the
country.
We came all this way,
but there is nothing to
be found but junk from
other villages!
Why is it junk just
because it is imported?
I guess there won't be
any new mushroom dishes
at the local restaurants
in the Hidden Leaf, then.
We have no choice.
We'll just have to
head back.
Uh...
That's Hinata...
Hey, Neji, look!
Hm?
Hinata!
[screaming]
Oh, hey, Neji.
Hello, Tenten.
What are you doing
all the way out here
in the forest?
Oh, what a coincidence!
I'm just here to
landscape the
mountainside.
That's some
coincidence...
A girl in this day and
age cutting grass on a
mountainside by herself
with a traditional scythe.
Is something
wrong, Hinata?
[sigh]
Uh...
You were following us?
Yes. I saw everyone
leaving to go look for
matsutake mushrooms, so
I tagged along.
I have the day off,
too. And you looked like
you were having so much
fun that I couldn't resist!
Maybe I shouldn't have
but I ended up following
your group.
Just 'ended up', huh?
But you do realize that
you didn't have to follow
us in secret, right?
You could've called
out to us at any time!
Oh, I, uh...
Hinata wasn't following
us, she was following
Naruto! That's why you
didn't try harder to
get our attention,
isn't it?
Um... Well...
You know, I kind
just, um...
Gotcha! Then let
us help you out,
okay?
Huh?
Of course, it's entirely
up to you whether or not
things work out with
Naruto...
But maybe we can help
you overcome some of
your shyness.
Right, Neji?
Sure. If this is something
that will help Hinata,
then you can count me in.
Wow, you guys.
Thank you so much.
Oh...
You guys! Where
have you been?
Sorry, Lee! We
had something to
deal with.
Oh! Hinata!
Oh! Hey, there, Hinata!
What are you doing way
out here?
Naruto... I, uh...
Relax, relax!
And just try to
act natural!
N-Natural...
I came up here to the
mountain to do some
laundry.
What's natural
about that?!
Well, I was using this
outfit to symbolize
Mother Nature.
That's the wrong kind
of acting and the wrong
kind of natural!
I can see you're as
natural as ever,
Hinata!
I'm natural?
I just knew it! I
should've symbolized a
big natural monument
like the Jomon Cedar!
Right now, all you're
symbolizing is the
loss of your mind.
It's hopeless! Her brain
just doesn't function
correctly when she's
around Naruto.
Hey, whatever happened
to the matsutake mushroom
hunt?
We have all been talking
about it, and unfortunately
it appears that we will have
to call it quits.
We've only found one
this whole day! Maybe
I'll just go grab some
ramen.
Yeah, I think I'll
head back and get
some lunch, too.
[sigh]
Oh well, that's
too bad!
Oh, no! We just got
Hinata to join
everyone!
If we don't do something
as a group, Hinata will
never come out of her shell!
Guy Sensei, hunting for
matsutake mushrooms is
great training!
We should continue the
hunt for them! There's
just no question about it!
Well, I really am
craving some...
Going home without
gathering some
would be a shame...
All right, everyone!
We're going to have
a competition to see who
can find the most
mushrooms!
[sigh]
So the search for
matsutake mushrooms
begins, but...
Yeah, but if you ask me,
without question the best
way to serve mushrooms is
in ramen!
C'mon Hinata, just
go and talk to Naruto.
Um, yeah, okay...
Naruto, do you think
that maybe we could-
Sakura! Since this is
a team competition,
let's team up!
[whining]
He's not listening
to me!
We've got no choice
but to gather more
matsutake mushrooms
than them!
If we win...
I didn't know matsutake
mushrooms were this good!
You're so awesome,
Hinata!
Yeah! And then that self-
confidence will help her
finally start talking to
Naruto!
Let's go for it, Hinata!
Uh... Right!
Everyone is so
motivated to
win this!
Then I will have to
do my absolute best!
So...
Come on, everyone,
let us go!
What's with
that outfit?!
I figured that this would
be the bare minimum required
to go out on a hunt!
You're just wasting time
and energy! And that's
the wrong kind of hunt,
anyway!
And why did you have to
make Hinata and me both
dress up like hunting
dog as well?!
Okay, then what
about this?
It is seven o'clock!
Time for the show to
begin! Say hello to
Kyouko!
That's the wrong
kind of hunter!
No, I was focusing
more on the idea of
confidence!
You're getting way to
obscure! And that would
interest moms more than the
kids who are watching this!
Fine, then!
How about a few
monster hunters!
The show's sponsors
aren't paying me
enough to deal with
this!
All right, that's it!
I've had enough of this!
[screaming]
Since this is our
first hunt, I don't
actually know what
the best strategy is.
Let's go check
out what everyone
else is doing.
Here goes!
Ugh! I haven't
found anything!
Man, these matsutake
mushrooms sure are shy!
It appears that Shikamaru's
group has been utilizing
Ino's Mind-Transfer Jutsu.
Yeah, with that...
Ino can take over the
minds of animals and
have them do what she
wants.
Wait, the mind...
Of course, that is
it! The mind!
Huh? What's
that mean?
In order to figure out
how to coax the mushrooms
out of hiding, we need to
get inside their heads
and think like they do!
Neji, Hinata, I will
need you to help me out.
Hey, what about me?
You would be useless!
I'd be useless?
No offense. I only
need Neji and Hinata
for this job.
What? You need me?
What the-?!
Hey, Matsuko, I am going
to a party with some
people from Mountain Yam
University tomorrow!
Nameko and Donko are
already coming, as well.
But we really need to
bring along one more.
Hey, so, would
you come with us?
Oh, come on, Matsuko,
do not be that way.
Quit acting so shy!
If you came along, you
would be the life of the
party, I just know that
you would!
Lee! What are
you doing?!
I was only trying to think
like a shy matsutake mushroom
and to create an inviting
atmosphere where they
would be comfortable
with joining us.
If that was all it took,
then every last college in
the country would be filled
to brim with mushrooms.
And why did you have
to make us dress up
yet again?!
We three are the only
ones who have mushroom-
shaped heads!
Hey, don't call us
mushroom-heads!
Oh, Matsuko,
you poor baby!
Huh?
You...
I know exactly how you
feel deep down inside...
I really don't like
it when girls are so
tentative!
I know because I'm very
shy, as well. And I just
can't stand it!
Hinata...
She's talking
about herself...
I'm going to try my
absolute hardest to be
as brave as I can.
And I'm finally going
to talk to Naruto, too!
Talk to me about what?
I was about to head
back. What are you
guys up to?
Oh, well, you know, we
were just kind of...
[screaming]
Hinata!
Naruto, you idiot!
What's wrong?
What did I do?
I don't care anymore!
I just can't do it!
Wow, what an
incredible tumble!
It's kinda like a
metaphor for her
life right now!
Hinata, hang on!
[groaning]
[gasp]
That's...
Well, bon appetit!
Too bad Hinata was the
only one who ended up
finding a mushroom.
It's good thing that
even one is plenty
delicious, then!
You did awesome,
Hinata! Great job!
Thanks, Naruto...
And so, the kinda successful
hunt for matsutake mushrooms
granted Hinata a little
more courage.
You know, Hinata, I've
been meaning to tell you
something for a while now.
[gasp]
You have?
With your hairstyle and
personality, you're
starting to remind me
of Bushy-Brow.
Oh...
Huh? What's the matter?
[growling]
Naruto!
What?! What
did I do?!
Everyone, no matter
how calm, gets angry
sometimes, right?
[yelling]
I've had about all I can
take from this village!
So give me some money
and safe passage to
another one, pronto-
or else!
Help me! Someone
do something!
Do not worry!
Huh?!
We are on the scene,
so relax! You will
be safe now!
Hey, that's the ninja
who can't use ninjutsu,
isn't it?
How can he save
that guy?!
Easy! I do not need to
use ninjutsu to stop a
petty criminal such as this
one! I will use genjutsu!
Genjutsu?!
Oh no, not
again.
Come on now, buddy, stop
being unreasonable and
think of your poor mother
back home!
Just what would
she say?!
I knew it.
Huh?
It is not too late!
Do not make her suffer
anymore!
Please ma'am, come
over and talk to him.
No way... My
mother is here?
Why does it always
have to be me?
Just look at her! Do
you not see how depressed
this poor old woman is
feeling right now!
It is your fault!
It's your fault!
[groaning]
"Lee and Neji Part Ways"
I've had enough!
In every single episode,
you subject me to the
worst humiliations!
Neji...
Please, calm
down, Neji!
How can I calm down?!
On the matsutake mushroom
hunt alone, you made me
dress up like a 70's singer,
a dog, some monster hunter,
and even a mushroom!
But that was not just
any mushroom! It was
Matsutake Matsuko's
good friend and fellow
sophomore from
Toadstool University!
And her name was Donko
Shiitake!
That is not the issue!
Forget it! I'm done
with all this silliness!
Neji...
Wow, I never thought
Neji would do that.
It sounds to me like
he's really angry.
To be perfectly honest,
this entire time...
...I had no idea
he felt that way.
What?! How could you
not know that?!
In every single skit you've
ever done, you've put him
in silly roles and weird
costumes!
He's just been
putting up with it!
I always thought he was
on board with everything
we did.
If only you'd take some
of that endless optimism
and apply it to some more
noble pursuits, Lee.
I know what I must do!
I will keep him out of the
more colorful roles and cast
him as the main character!
You're not getting it!
Wouldn't it be better
just to apologize, Bushy
Brow?
Yeah, it seems like
you're risking the loss
of a close friend here.
Perhaps...
I know what I must do.
I will apologize then seal
away my genjutsu forever!
They're just skits.
Did you hear
that, Kabuto?
Yes. Every word.
Lee's actually going
to choose to seal away
his genjutsu techniques!
But they're not genjutsu,
they're just skits, Lord
Orochimaru.
It's infuriating how
many times that genjutsu
has defeated us.
You're starting to
infuriate me, Lord
Orochimaru.
But without his genjutsu,
Lee would be nothing more
than an old man at a bar
bragging about his glory days.
That doesn't even
make any sense!
This is going to
be just perfect!
Meanwhile, at
Neji's house...
That Lee! I can't
even stand to look
at him now.
N-Neji...
Hm?
Yes, Hinata? What
can I do for you?
Um... Actually, I
have a big favor
to ask you.
A big favor?
Yes.
I want to learn how to
stop being so introverted
and shy. And I could use
your help with that.
Why, of course,
Hinata. It's my
pleasure.
Simply tell me
what it is that
you'd like me to
do.
I realized something
on the matsutake
mushroom hunt.
When I'm able to project
myself into something
external, it's easier to
say what's in my heart.
That day, the external
thing was just a mushroom,
and yet...
Uh, okay...
But still, if I use
that as a starting
point...
Then I believe that I
can finally learn to
overcome my shyness!
Again, what
exactly do you
need from me?
Please...
I want you to be my
acting partner, Neji!
[groaning]
Listen closely, Lee.
You need to apologize
to Neji and bury the
hatchet with him or
you might lose him
as a friend forever!
[sigh]
Yes, she is right.
Aw, you seem sad.
Wait, that voice!
Orochimaru! Why
are you here?!
Come on! Have you
forgotten my character's
motivation?
I'm here to destroy
the Leaf, of course!
You've forgotten that
more than anyone else in
recent memory Lord
Orochimaru.
I never learn, do you?
I will not let you harm
the village!
Impressive confidence.
But do you truly believe
that you have what it
takes to stop me?
Absolutely!
[charging yell]
[grunting]
That is enough!
Great Leaf Hurricane!
[grunting]
[screaming]
How can this be?!
Lord Orochimaru was
pulled in so easily!
Don't worry, Kabuto.
[gasp]
Ah! This is genjutsu!
Uhh, a skit?
If you really think you
stand a chance, go ahead.
But I know you're nothing
more than a little baby
who hates his vegetables!
Ugh! There is only
one way out of this
now!
I really do have to try
to increase my daily
fiber intake.
Because that is the
hidden secret to a
truly successful diet.
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
But, I have forsaken
genjutsu so that I can
patch everything up with
Neji! I cannot fight back!
It actually worked!
Without his ridiculous
skits, Lee has lost his
ability to fight!
Without his genjutsu
he's nothing! Now I just
have to deliver the
finishing blow!
Tenten, Neji...
What do I do?
You need me?
Yes.
Please, Mr. Mayo, I
need you by my side!
What are you
talking about?
How can you say that you
need me when you and
Saucestein of the Sauce
Clan are inextricably linked!
Plus everyone knows that
you've also been with Bono
the Bonito and Sean the
Seaweed since forever.
Yes, but...
Konomi...
Huh?
Please, don't try to make
me stray away from you
anymore. Bye.
No!
I've always wanted to
say this to you, but I've
just been to afraid to!
I never ever stopped
thinking about you!
Konomi...
What the heck is this
scene?! What are we in,
some kind of soap opera?
And why would there be
drama between mayonnaise
and an okonomiyaki?!
Even if it is for Hinata,
the writing in this scene
is just awful!
That was so
wonderful, Neji!
What?!
I don't think I could've
made so much progress if
you weren't so good.
I'm just not used to
this kind of stuff.
Yes, I understand.
Someday I want to be
able to actually say
all that to the actual
person...
...instead of just
saying it to a bottle
of mayonnaise.
But, anyway, thank
you very much for all
of your help, Neji!
Sure, Hinata.
And I'm going to have
to give my thanks to
Lee and Tenten the
next time I see
them, too.
What? Those two?
Oh yes! I never would've
been able to ask this favor
of you just a couple of
years ago.
Building closer relationships
with all your friends has made
you so much more dependable
and so kind.
[gasp]
Neji, can we do the
scene one more time?
I'm sorry, Hinata.
Huh?
I just remembered
something I have
to do.
Oh! Sure, go
right ahead!
And now, it is time
to finish this!
Lee!
Just what are you
doing?! You should've
ended this with genjutsu
in a heartbeat!
Neji...
But I swore that I would
seal away my genjutsu.
This isn't like you.
But if you're still
willing to let me
help you...
Then I'll be more than
happy to pitch in and
do whatever I can.
I just... had a
little thinking
to do.
Neji...
Neji!
I'll just help you
out a little bit here
and there. It's no
big deal!
Oh, Neji!
Thank you, Neji!
My eyes! It's
in my eyes!
No! Lord Orochimaru!
Mayo on my veggies!
Even a little baby
like me will eat
his veggies now!
Whatever! Let's
just take these
guys down, Lee!
Right!
Let us go!
[screaming]
Neji...
Don't say anything.
I'm...I'm sorry.
Neji!
And so, Neji showed Lee
that he'd come to understand
his genjutsu, at least a
little.
Come on, buddy! Just
think of your poor mother
back home, worrying!
Please, ma'am...
Come over here and
talk to him, would you?
But as nearly everyone
else thought would happen,
Neji ended up regretting it
almost immediately.
Ugh... I should've known.
The title's for next time
are: "We are Here to Welcome
Gaara!" and "The Ultimate
Autumn Diet!"
Neji, let us keep our
momentum going!
Looks like I won't
have to dress up
at all!
You could not be more
wrong! For certain scenes
to be conveyed properly,
we need Nejie, Nejio,
Nejitine, Nejinia.
I have about eight
hundred characters
lined up for you to
play!
But why?! Why do
they all have to
be girls?!