The colors of fall are now
at their most vibrant. That
means it's the perfect time
to relax at the hot springs!
[grunting]
It's useless! I can't
find a spring anywhere!
Wait, are you trying to
dig your own hot spring,
Orochimaru?
That's right! I've been
running myself ragged
digging around for one
all week,
but I still haven't
found one anywhere!
[chuckling]
Well, that settles it.
I'll just have to...
[laughing]
"Nothing Beats
Mixed Bathing!"
[sigh]
I'm pooped.
That mission was brutal.
I'm pretty worn out, too.
Less talking,
more sleeping.
I wouldn't mind a
bit of rest, myself.
This is no time to be
taking it easy! We must
hurry home and start
training feverishly so
that we will be ready
for the next mission!
Not this time. Don't
forget, warriors need
their rest, too!
Guy Sensei?
It's come to my attention
that a brand new hot spring
has just opened up.
Conveniently enough, it's
just outside of the Leaf
Village.
I think you should all
go check it out. Your next
mission is: "Give your body
a nice long rest!"
And that's how Rock Lee
and his ninja pals found
themselves in front of the
newly-opened "Orochi
Hot Springs."
Look at that!
It says that all the baths
here are from 100% natural
spring waters!
Hm? "Orochi" Hot Springs?
Oh, come on.
Not him again.
Yes! Him again! Who
else would it be?
[laughing]
Look at them. Those
fools don't suspect
a thing.
Are you kidding?
It's exactly the
opposite!
Lord Orochimaru
you've made them
more suspicious
then ever!
Why did you have
to name this place
the "Orochi Hot
Springs?!"
It couldn't be
more obvious!
This must be one of
Orochimaru's traps!
I bet he's planning to
get us to relax, then
attack while our guard
is down!
What?! Curses!
Hold on a second.
I welcome you, one and
all to the Okuchichi
Hot Springs!
Did you say "Okuchichi"?
Yes.
This isn't a "ro,"
it's the kanji that
reads "kuchi".
That's why were called the
"Okuchichi Hot Springs!"
[giggling]
That's way too far-
fetched. They'll never
believe it.
I see it now! It's
read as "Okuchichi."
What?! That's nuts!
Well, think about it.
If this was one of
Orochimaru's tricks,
he wouldn't be so
incredibly dense as to
actually use his own
name!
That makes sense!
He's dumb, but he's
not that dumb!
I have to agree! He may
be a failure, but it is
not like he is a complete
blundering idiot!
Right?
You'll pay for that!
Come now! Go relax and
enjoy our beautiful
outdoor bath!
Whoa! It is a-
It's a mixed
gender bath!
What?! Seriously?!
As I'm sure you've gathered,
a mixed gender bath is set
up where the men and women
don't have separate bathing
areas. Instead, they bathe
and enjoy the water together.
Ahhh! M-M-M-M-M-M-
Mixed gender?!
A mixed gender
bath with Sakura?!
Sakura and I in
the same hot spring?!
[laughing]
What should we do?
Take turns bathing
or something?
We could, but there's
not much time left before
dinner, so...
I know! The Transformation
Jutsu will solve this!
Naruto!
On it! Check
this out!
Neji!
Hey, what do you
think you're-!
And finally me!
See? Look! We are all
girls! We can go in
the bath together!
Uhh, I don't
think so.
You know, in a weird
way, he might actually
be on to something.
Huh?
What if you and I
use the technique,
too?
[gasp]
Oh, I see! Nice!
Good thinking!
[sigh]
They had to put towels
on? It figures. I
shouldn't have gotten
my hopes up.
This plain setting is
far too dull for my
tastes. We should
have flowers.
But these outfits should
brighten up the shot.
They had to put on swan
tutus before we were
allowed to film.
If that's your idea
of a flower, I'm
outta here!
What if they wore those
swan tutus while washing
each other's backs at
the same time?
Wash, wash!
Rub, rub!
I'm not sure what I'm
supposed to be seeing
here. Who on earth does
this appeal to?
That was a relaxing
bath, was it not?
Man! You said it! And
the foods great here,
too!
Plenty more where that
came from, so eat up!
And as your stomach's
take in this feast,
feast your eyes on the
dinnertime show!
How humiliating!
Why me?!
For some reason, I feel
a strong connection with
that dancing girl.
You look perplexed,
Neji. Has the dancing
girl managed to capture
your heart?
What?! No! Don't
be ridiculous!
Oooh! He wants to
give her kissy kissy!
[chuckling]
I think the time
has finally come!
Oh? The time for what
has come exactly?
Wait a minute!
Is it time for
more food?!
Wrong! Neither!
The time has finally
come to punish you
pesky little brats!
Fooled you,
didn't I?!
Orochimaru?!
I knew it!
It's too late! You've
fallen into my trap!
You're all too relaxed
and loosened up being
at my luxurious resort!
That's what you
think! You're mine!
Rasengan!
[gasp]
[chuckling]
I see that my relaxing
hot springs really helped
your chakra unwind.
Chakra can't
unwind like that!
Byakugan!
No good. I can't
see what kind of
soup it is.
The soup's not
important!
He's right. The hot
springs relaxed our
chakra so much, we
can't use our jutsu!
Huh. I guess chakra
can relax. Who knew?
You're finished! You
think you stand a chance
against me without your
jutsu?
Ha! This hot spring
will serve as your
grave!
Since I have never had
my own ninjutsu, I can
still fight with tai-
jutsu!
Lee!
Do not worry, Tenten.
I have a secret fighting
style that is a perfect
fit for hot springs!
Karaoke-Fu!
What the-?
I think ping-pong
is more "hot springy",
personally.
Interesting challenge.
Yes! I'll play along
with it!
Looks like they're
out for blood.
Which one of them
do you think is
going to sing first?
And what song?
My selection will be,
the theme song to that
other famous ninja anime:
Play "Courage 200%"!
They're actually
gonna sing!
I foresee a 200%
chance of death.
What's gotten into you?!
Have you no pride as a
Leaf Village Ninja, Lee?!
But singing what he
wants is a small
victory! Go!
Hmph! Bringing out the
big guns already, huh?
No matter. It's nothing
compared to my selection
of a song from that
famous idol group!
Heavy Boa-tation!
Lord Orochimaru, you're
risking defeat and a
lawsuit! Your voice will
tarnish the image of those
poor girls and their
music forever!
Wait just a minute!
Are you sure about
all this? If you sing
while on the air
without licensing
the songs first...
I am ready when
you are!
I'm going to
enjoy this!
[gasp]
Suddenly, the karaoke
machine mysteriously
exploded.
You see? Fate's
telling you not
to sing!
There are mysterious
forces far more powerful
than our own at work here!
It would appear that we
need to pick an alternate
way to fight that is still
theme appropriate.
I would have preferred
avoiding doing something
like this on a kid's show,
but here we are.
No way! You're
breaking the rules!
Baseball Fist!
Don't do it! Think
about it! Primetime
isn't ready for
something like that!
Stopping now is
not an option!
Orochi High vs. Leaf
Academy. It's 0-0, bottom
of the ninth, two outs,
and the bases are loaded.
Orochi High could end
the whole thing right
here.
Big brother...
The count's 0-2,
Will the next pitch
be the last?!
I have to win this game!
I have to win it for my
dear, beloved sick sister!
You have my empathy,
but regardless of your
circumstances. I will
not hold back!
At the mound, Rock
Lee winds up for
the pitch.
And throws!
No matter what it takes,
I will win this! For her!
And he's hit
by the pitch!
[screaming]
Yes! I won! I am
unstoppable!
What? No! That's not
how the game works, you
idiot! The bases were
loaded!
They scored!
My team won!
You cannot possibly be
serious! That was only
the outcome of the ball
game!
The real battle between
you and me is about
breaking the rules!
What the heck?!
You lousy cheater!
[laughing]
That does it!
Summoning Jutsu!
What now? Has this
turned into a giant
monster battle?
Orochimaru,
you coward!
Hnnh! I'll crush the
life out of you for
sure this time, Rock
Lee!
Freeze.
Who are you two?
What do you want?
From the cheapest day
spa to the most well
hidden gems throughout
the land...
We fight to protect the
healing waters and relaxing
atmosphere of all hot springs!
The hot spring inspectors:
The Spa Rangers!
The minerals in your
water...They were added
and not naturally occurring!
You're coming
with us!
Move it!
Huh? Hey, wait
just a second!
Justice is served.
Hi-ho Silver!
I won't forget this!
You're gonna pay!
Lord Orochimaru!
And that was that.
Orochimaru may have
won the battle, but
he lost the war.
Oh boy...
Today, Orochimaru is busy
plotting a way to defeat
our Rock Lee...
You don't say...
Take a look at this. I've
created a most dastardly
"Rock Lee Hotel", to trap
that eyebrowed eyesore
once and for all!
[chuckling]
Now what should
I use as bait?
A stamp card for a
curry restaurant that
needs just one more
free meal?
Or maybe an all-you-
can-drink on your
birthday coupon?
Oh, the very evil
things I come up
with!
[gasp]
You've got to be kidding
me! My own birthday was
the middle of last week
and I completely
forgot about it!
"October 27th was
Orochimaru's Birthday!"
[sigh]
Another year goes
by, another year
older...
My youth is over. I'm
aging. My skin isn't as
firm and radiant as it
once was.
Wait a minute! That's
not the real tragedy
here! The real tragedy
is that not one single,
solitary soul remembered
my birthday! How could
they?!
How could they, I say?!
Lord Orochimaru!
What's going on?!
Kabuto! You callous
fiend! You've forgotten
something very, very
important!
Something of great
significance happened
last week! What was it?!
I did? Great
significance...
Oh, that's right! Last
week was the premiere of
the first episode of "Make-
Our Fall in Love Picking
Chestnuts on Mount
Sarukani" and I forgot
to set my DVR! I need to
see if there's an encore!
Ahhh...
No, you twit! What happened
can't be compared to some
romantic rubbish on television.
Manda! I know you remember
what happened last week,
right? Something of absolute
and high-level importance
that starts with a "B"?
[hissing]
B Vitamins.
Not even close!
Hey, B vitamins are
important to a healthy
lifestyle.
I'm not talking about
health! This is ridiculous!
How could you be this far
off?!
Something that starts
with a "b" that's much
more important than
vitamins!
Bulbs? Bulbs
are important!
If you're going to bring
up lighting, at least use
LEDs! They use much less
electricity and they're
better for the environment!
It was my birthday
you idiots! It-Was-
My-Birth-Day!
Oh, is that right?
Ahh, wait a minute.
I'll make Lee suffer
the same anguish.
Let's see. Lee's birthday
is coming up soon. If I'm
not mistaken, it's November
27th.
He too, will suffer the
loneliness, the misery,
the agony, oh the anguish
of having his birthday
forgotten by every last
single one of his little
ninja pals!
[laughing]
Whoa! What in the
world are you wearing?
Oh, you noticed that,
did you? I can't in good
conscience ask Kabuto for
any help, as that useless
nitwit forgot my birthday,
too. So now, I'll be playing
that fool's part along with
my own!
Lord Orochimaru. I think
that's enough exposition
for the time being.
[laughing]
You're right. First,
I will need my time-
release chakra.
I'll hide it in his shoes
where it will wait until
it's time to strike. On
the morning of his birthday,
as he walks merrily
along, I'll have my
vengeance.
I am walking merrily
along! Happy Birthday
to me!
Ow!
Oh, no!
After that agonizing
torture, I'll set a
black cat to cross
his path.
[meowing]
Impending doom
awaits me!
And finally, when he
looks up to the sky...
He'll see the bad-luck
star shining down on
him as clear as can be!
The bad-luck star
has cursed my
birthday!
He'll have the most
miserable birthday
morning of his life,
and he'll have me to
thank for it! Take
that, Rock Lee!
Your plan is so
boring it put me
to sleep.
Put a cork in it! Piling
up one annoyance after
another can do plenty of
damage!
[gasp]
Whoa! Orochimaru,
what the-?! Get your
pervy hands off my
shoes!
This is bad, my Lord.
If you're found out now,
the plan is ruined!
You've gotta talk
your way out of this!
Sorry! I was- It's
getting colder now, and
I was warming up everyone's
shoes. That way, you won't
catch a cold! Understand?
It's nothing "pervy".
That doesn't make
any sense at all,
you weirdo!
[screaming]
Those jerks are in for
a big surprise if they
think I'll give up that
easily.
I've still got lots of
other options. On the
morning of his birthday,
I'll make him step in a
pile of dog poo!
Are we clear? I want you
to squeeze out plenty of
land mines on Lee's morning
running course!
Drop as many squishy
deuces as you can!
And you're feeding
him a month out?
[growling]
[screaming]
I won't be broken.
Nothing will stop me!
I've got plenty more in
store for him.
Just you wait!
[snickering]
You happy birthday lands
on the anniversary of
Buddha's death!
And even worse
than that...
Actually, that's
Friday the 13th.
[laughing]
Lord Orochimaru. If
it's the 13th, then
technically it's not
even his birthday.
Understand?
What else would ruin
someone's birthday?
If only there was an
easily accessible
resource I could- I've
got it! I'll search the
internet for the answer!
Genius!
Worst birthday
memories ever.
Let's see here... Hah!
Here we go! "None of my
subordinates remembered
my birthday this year.
Even when I asked,
"Hey, didn't you forget
something important?"
They were still stumped.
All they could talk
about were vitamins and
light bulbs and other
stuff...
Wait a minute, this
is my blog! I hate
everything right now!
Lord Orochimaru!
Do you really have
a blog?!
Ah, I see. It makes
sense now. Of all the
terrible things that
can happen on your
birthday, this is
the absolute worst!
Thank goodness! The
wait is finally over!
We are back onscreen!
Tell me about it. I
wasn't even sure we'd
show up again.
Hey, check it out!
A new restaurant's
opening up soon!
Sweet, it's a
ramen place!
Open November 27th. The
first 10 customers get
all-you-can-eat ramen!
Awesome!
I'm lining up first
thing that morning!
And with that,
it begins.
You know, I bet Choji
will want to come
along, too. We should
invite him.
No can do, Choji said
he's going over there
that day. Take a look!
Whoa! Another promo
on November 27th?
How odd.
Wait. We're talking
about November 27th?
Yes, we are.
What is up, Neji?
Huh. That's funny. The
Hyugas are holding a
memorial service that
very day.
It should've been the
day before, but for some
reason, they weren't able
to book the venue
and had to push
it back. Odd.
Wait a second. Now that
you mention it, Lady
Tsunade's "Ladies' Get
Together" is that day,
too. I was planning on
attending it. I knew that
date sounded familiar.
So everyone has
plans that day?
This doesn't make any
sense. What's so special
about November 27th?
[laughing]
I'll tell you what's
special about November
27th! It's Fishing Day!
Fishing day?
Yes! It's the fishiest
day of them all! The
village fishing holes
are letting us catch
as much as we want
that day!
I see. So there's
another thing on
the 27th!
Actually, I invited Kakashi
along, too. But he's lining
up for this particular
event, instead.
I can't believe so
many things are
happening on that day.
Agh!
I almost completely
forgot about another
thing that happens
that day!
November 27th is
my birthday!
That means... Do
not tell me that
you all...
[chuckling]
That's right. I'm
behind every last one
of these events.
Now no one will be able
to attend your birthday
party. They've all made
plans already! You'll
be all alone, crying
tears of loneliness
into your crummy
birthday cake!
That means... Do not
tell me that you all...
You all conveniently
made unbreakable plans
for that day so that
Sakura and I can spend
my birthday together,
just the two of us,
like some kind of date?!
Agh! What's wrong
with you?! Why are
you so positive?!
And on the night of my
birthday, when Sakura
and I are all alone...
It will be like the
pages of those
risque manga...
Hey, Lee. Happy
Birthday, lover.
I'm your present.
Unwrap me!
I have to admit, I am
a bit embarrassed! But
I am also so, so very
happy!
That's crossing the line,
Bushy-Brow! Sakura would
never do something like
that for you!
Not even on your
birthday!
What do you know?
Lee's birthday is on
November 27th, as
well. Imagine that.
[laughing]
Enjoy yourself while
you can, Rock Lee.
Because...
Well, let me put it
this way. You'll get
a present, but it won't
be that Sakura girl!
It will be me!
I see. So you arranged
to be delivered to him
on the 27th? Very
clever, my Lord.
Indeed! At the height
of his despair. As Rock
Lee is crying, Orochimaru
will pop out of this
present and cheer him
up!
[laughing]
What's this package?
I heard something
laughing inside.
Must be some
kind of prank.
Ah, it's creeping me
out. Let's just trash
it!
Hnh?!
Agh!
Hey! What are you
doing! Stop it! I'm
not garbage! Quit
knocking me around!
[screaming]
Huh?
Surprise! I know it's a
little late, but still.
We all wanted to do
something extra special
for you. Happiest of
Birthdays, Lord
Orochimaru! We wish
you all the best!
Kabuto... What's the
big idea? Why didn't
you do this on the
right day?
Because you were
out wandering that
day, my Lord...
You were in the
mountains looking
for a hot spring.
Remember?
I had no idea
where you were!
Ohh...
Well, like they always
say: all's well that ends
well, right, Orochimaru?
Happy Birthday!
Thank you so
much, everyone!
Next time we have "Sakura's
My Nurse!" and "One Vote
For Rock Lee!" I hope that
you enjoy them!
Hey, Lord Orochimaru's
supposed to be doing the
preview, don't cut him
off like that!
It's all right.
Eh?
We're celebrating my
birthday, remember? I'm
so happy. I want everyone
to share in my joy.
Just this once.
Lord Orochimaru,
that's not how a
villain should talk.
Wait. I'm the
villain?!