(Narrator)
Today's Rock Lee is starting!
But this episode has a bit of
a different flavor...
(Narrator)
So buckle up, because
today's show is tying
in with that hit new movie-
This is bad! I
totally forgot
to buy this week's
issue of Jump!
I hope they
still have some!
[gasp]
Yes! There is
one left..!
Oh! Tenten!
Lee, you too?
It's a good thing it
was you I ran into!
Anyone else, and it
would've been a
serious tug-of-war.
Agreed! Talk about good
luck-- Now we'll both be
able to read it! Here,
let me take a loo--
[smack]
What was that for?
My question exactly!
Ladies first, Lee.
You'll have to
wait until I'm
done with it!
What the--!? You are
the one who is always
saying that gender
shouldn't matter!
You're gonna read
it on the toilet..!
So what!? You're
gonna read it in
the bath!
Better than
stinking it up!
I am not reading a
water damaged comic!
oh would you let
go!? This issue
has info on the
movie!!
I know! That is
exactly why--
I want the latest
details now!!
Ahhh!
Huh?!
"Road to Guy"
[groan]
What just happened?
It felt like the
world turned inside
out...
Do not panic, Tenten!
Believe me, this has
happened before!
[panting]
Let us just stay calm
and find some water!
No no no,
you just had
heat stroke.
Hey, what are
you two doing
here?
Shino? Boy, good
timing. Something
really weird just
happen--
Not as weird as
your outfit!!!
What do you mean
by that? I'm just
being FABULOUS as
usual.
I may be a ninja
but I don't blend
into the background!
That's the kinda
man I am!
I am green with
envy! You are out-
pizazzing the star
of the show!
Lee, you and Naruto
are all the pizazz
this show can handle.
So like, did Shino
get a concussion or
something..?
Don't...stare...
Something wrong..?
You're not usually
so shy, Kiba...
Huh!?
For goodness sake,
I'll answer for you!
But don't think I'm
doing it to be nice
though, you guys!
I can't depend on
anyone else here, so I
don't have a choice!
Hinata is snapping
a people!?
That's impossible!
What's wrong with
everyone!?
(Shikamaru)
There a problem?
-Huh!?
Shikamaru! Oh thank
goodness you're-- Huh!?
Oh jeez, how am I
s'posed to be the
straight man...anymore.
What a day!
I mean, did I
clean up in
there or what!?
Yay! We're off to
make the world a
better place!
We're off to fight
evil, doncha know!
What's next? The
whole world's gone
topsy turvy...
I know what to
do! At times like
this, there's only
one way out!!
Huh?
Alrighty then.
Night-night.
We're not in a
dream Leeeeee!!
Indeed.
Be serious! This is
not a normal crisis!
If we don't find
out what happened
we could be stuck
here forever!!
Right! Let's
move out then!
Where to?
To find Neji!
(Lee)
We will need help if
we are going to figure
out what happened!
Yeah, but...
It is okay! No matter
how much the world's
changed, our friendship
is unshakable!
(Neji)
Not a chance
in hell!!
(Lee)
Huh!?!?!?
(Neji)
The Dark Emperor
appears!
Me and my friends
from a previous life
must face him in
battle!
I can't abandon this
fight-- the fate of
the world hands in
the balance!
Our...friendship...
I can't believe
Neji's angsty
teen gamer...
This is a dead end!
We'll have to look
for clues on our own!
(Hizashi Hyuga)
Neji, I'm leaving
your dinner out here!
[gasp]
Hold on a minute!
I am just realizing
something...
What are you
talking about?
I knew it!
Neji's ramen!
It is exactly
the same!
What?
And the bizarre situation we've
found ourselves in, it's all
just like the promotional
material for the movie!
So you're saying...
I do not know
how or why...
but in that
instant...
...our wish to know
what the movie would
be like was granted
by this issue of Jump!
Maybe we've been
transported into
the world of the
movie!
You really think
it's...possible?
You ready, Tenten!?
Let's do this, Lee!
[grunts]
How come it
didn't work?
Everything was
exactly the same.
No! One key element
was missing!
Huh?
The first time, we both
longed to see the sneak
peek with every fiber
of our being!
Our should burned with
passion, and we both
refused to let each other
have the first l
ook!
Like this!!
Haaaaaaaaaaa!
(Tenten)
Cut it out! You're
going to rip it!
I am sorry...
I hate to admit it,
but you might be
on to something...
We can't just
follow a script,
though. We need
to FEEL it.
A script...!?
That is a
brilliant idea!
What on earth are
you wearing...?
I know just what to
do! Script revision
plan... go!
Huh?
If we do not have
enough passion, we
will just physically
alter the situation!
That's way too
literal, Lee!
It'll never work!
I will make it
work! I am not
staying in this
world another minute!
(Lee)
The Neji I know is
arrogant and wears
boxers...
(Lee)
But he is also a
man who values
friendship!
(Lee)
I am bringing
that Neji back!
What do you think?
Did it work?
Okay, you can come
on out, Neji!
Behold the
explosion of youth!
What are you,
crazy!? He looks
just like Guy
Sensei now!
One...two...
three... four...
Lee, what did
you do!?
I am not sure!
I was concentrating
with all my might on
Neji, but I guess I
missed the mark a little.
Anyway, it looks
like this method
is effective!
Huh?
(Lee)
Next up..! A quiet
hard worker who never
neglected her training-
-and Kiba and Shino,
her loyal friends!
Come back...!
Uhhh....
Behold! The
explosion of youth!
Not again!!!
Why do all your
mistakes turn them
into Guy Sensei!?
It looks like Guy Sensei
maintains an inordinately
large presence in my
subconscious...
Guy Sensei is always with
me... The stronger the
emotion... the more
entrenched he becomes...
Then you should probably
include Guy Sensei in
your thought and think
of everyone!
Oh--
go ahead, Lee.
Wish to return
to our old friends!
Hm.
I do not want this
to go on any longer...
I... I want to go
back to everyone!
[groan]
Tht was just like
the first time...
Huh!? Guys??
(Tenten)
You're back to normal!
Oh no! Everyone
is Guy Sensei now!
(Tenten)
Oh! Even the
normal villagers!?
Lee! This is
ridiculous!
What!? Guy Sensei!?
What are you
talking about?
It is me!
You wear the exact
same outfits...!!
Jeez, now your
face looks like
his, too!
Don't tell me!
Argh! I'm Guy
Sensei, too!
Make it stop!
Standards and practices is
gonna yank us off the air!
Behold! The explosion
of youth!
To youth!
Get away from me!
W-why is this
happening!?
I just wanted to
know about the movie,
is that so terrible!?
(Narrator)
Heh, of course not!
But you should know,
the movie is called-
"Naruto the Movie:
Road to Guy"
No it isn't! That's
not what the movie
is called at all!!!
(bird chirping)
Idiot..! Idiot..! Idiot..!
(Narrator)
Now then, we're all well
acquainted with the theatrics of
Team Guy here, but you have--
It's my theatrical
feature! Their theatrics!
(Narrator)
Well, Rock Lee and his
pals are just as excited
as you are!
Neji! Were you
able to score
some tickets!?
Oh yeah. The entire
Hyuga clan is planning
on attending it together.
Our advance-sale
tickets are in hand!
Neji! Lee! We've
got a problem!
What's wrong?
Something just went
down with Lady Tsunade!
What?!!
You're telling me that
the movie is still
missing a critical piece!?
And it's something
big, too...
That definitely
doesn't sound good!
It's lacking
something major!
So there is some kind
of problem with the film.
I wonder what...
"The Amazing True Story
of the Leaf Village Film
Festival"
Hmmm...
Gee. guys, I wonder
what's missing...
Ah!
I think I have
got this whole
problem figured
out!
[sirens]
[machine gun blasts]
[people screaming]
[gun blasts]
(thinking)
Man, I have got
no luck at all!
Here it is, Christmas
Eve, and I have got
to spend the night
rescuing my family!
[grunt]
[screaming]
What the heck
is going on?
Why did we suddenly
get thrown into this
stupid skit!?
But do you not
see, Tenten?!
The movie is missing
one vital thing! A
Hollywood action
sequence!
Carried out by a
gritty American
hero, overcoming all
the odds in style!
We don't want that
kinda mess! An
American action star?
(Tenten)
Naruto's supposed
to be the hero here!
(Tenten)
If you jump in like that,
you'll obliterate him!
It is fine! The
Movie's a compilation
of several arcs anyway!
Oh yeah! What if the
mortal enemy he's fighting
against eventually turns out
to be his most powerful ally!?
Are you out of
your mind, Lee!?
That'll ruin the
movie!!
It's true, Lee,
she's right.
Yo mean well, but
you're mixed up.
We haven't had a
single movie that's
lacked in blockbuster
action!
So then...! What
is missing, Neji!?
Of course! It's so
obvious... the one
thing we're lacking...
Oh Nejio, Nejio! Why
for art thou called
Nejio?
Oh, Hinaette... My life
were better ended, then
death prolonged..!
[swoon]
...wanting of
thy love!
But the youths belonged
to houses steeped in
ancient grudge...
Their misadventure
love doomed to fail,
they took matters
into their own hands!
[grunt]
Oh dearest Nejio!
I follow thee anon!
[grunt]
[church bells]
Woah, hold the
phone, why do
we need this?
A fair maiden and
fleeting romance!
Two soul mates
fading into starry
night!
It's obvious
what's missing! A
night of cinema
demands melodrama!
This is a summer
blockbuster! No one
wants to see a tear
jerker right now!
And we must bravely
shatter that mold!
It'll be the most
powerful film in
history! Breaking
hearts far and wide.
A timeless piece
that will forever
be a shining ex--
Go shine out in
the stratosphere,
will ya!?
I've been listening
to you guys, and you're
all totally clueless!
Kiba!? Then you
are saying you
have a better
idea!?
You bet we do!
Don't we, Hinata?
Um... well...
Maybe we're missing,
a ore innocent love,
you know..?
(Narrator)
Critics agree, it's the
greatest tearjerker of
the century...
(Narrator)
Number one in
all Nations!
-Leaf Times.
(Hinata)
With a young and
innocent love...
Huhhhh??
[chuckle]
A girl with no
courage... who
could only watch
him from afar...
But she had to
change... so he
would finally
notice her...
(Hinata)
Welcome home!
ARGH!
[sigh]
Huh!?
Whaaaa!?
Uh...!
(Hinata)
I got that for you!
Please use it on
your sore muscles!
(Hinata)
I've been watching you
since the day we met...
I still am...
[screams]
(Hinata)
I only have
eyes for you...
[distant scream]
Uch, that's not innocent
love! That's a horror
film about a stalker!
I'm not a
stalker!!
That does it then!
It's my turn, and
I'll settle this
once and for all!
Oh great, this
should be good.
We live in a world
of conflict! One where
ninja face one brutal
mission after another!
I know just what
we need.... Moe!
[laugh] Come on,
Akamaru!
[happy barking]
[happy laughing]
Oh, you..!
[happy barking]
Wait, only the
dog does cute!?
Well, duh! Of course!
What could be cuter
than a dog, Tente--
ARGGHHHHHH!!!
The audience
doesn't care!!!
Guys, your preoccupation
with the superficial
has only blinded you...
You've missed the one
crucial thing we've lacked.
Man's inner most
thinking made clear...
The voice of out
heart, singing out.
(thinking)
Wow, that's Shino
for you! He's so
deep...
(Shino)
The weather was awful the day
we filmed this scene. I can't
tell you how many takes we did.
We hit craft services for
lunch while we waited
for it to clear...
...the spread was pretty
light on veggies, I really
had my mind set on salad
that day....
You meant "audio
commentary!?"
There a problem
with that?
I don't even know
where to start!
You can't have audio
commentary in the
theatre!!!
Look, it's you.
Huh?! Yeah, you know, I really
wanted to get this scene just
right so we shot a ton of takes,
but at the end of the day--
Don't drag me
into this!!!
(sigh) I know that
we're missing something,
but what!?
You fools!
How can you ninnies
not see it!?
Orochimaru? What
are you doing here?
Just dropping in!
We saw you idiots
flailing about over
here and couldn't
resist..!
Wait, then you
know what the
movie is missing?
Silly child, you're
completely forgetting
the obvious, it seems.
Every film has one
essential element!
One that must never
be overlooked... The
most important thing
of all!
[gulps]
Annnd... action!
(Orochimaru)
I turn forty
this year.
I've spent my whole
career playing no-name
bit parts...
I always considered
myself dedicated to
the craft...
But one day I realized
that everyone around me
was half my age!
I saw them land starring
roles, while I just spun
my wheels!
I'm... fired!?
The thing is...
Everyone's having a
hard time working
with ya.
He's taking the
job way too seriously!
Cut! Cut, already!
Well, Orosuke's a nice
guy ad all, but sometimes
he's a big pushy...
(scream)
The camera's
over here...
(bar tender)
We're closing,
pal, go home.
(Orochimaru)
What'd you say
to me!?
(bar tender)
Alright! That's it!
(Orochimaru)
But even I found someone
who loved me...
I met the sheltered daughter
of some bigwig who ran a film
distribution company...
...and she fell for
a two-bit nobody like
me! Can you imagine?
He objected, of
course, so we ran
off...
...but before we'd had
a chance to create a
single memory together...
Even common courtesy
runs out eventually...
[sigh]
"Went back to my
parents house" eh?
Oh well...
Sweetheart...
sweetheart?!
You'e here... why?!
Why don't you
try out for this?
You asked your
father, didn't you?
I had to...
The first he did
was threaten to
disown me...
But begging on my
knees was a small
price to pay.
But why me...
I've seen first hand.
I know how brightly
you shine when you're
in front of the camera.
And I want that light
in my life every day!
[gasp]
Well this should be
good. Let's see what
you're made of, kid.
I'll do it! No
matter what it
takes!!
(crew member)
Standby, everybody!
Alright! Just watch,
my beloved! I'm going
to shine brighter than
the sun for you!
The hell!?
Wait a minute, is
this an anti-
piracy commercial?
Well, you'd be in
big trouble without.
Yeah I suppose so.
But what's that have
to do with the story?
Bravo, sir! You bring
such perspective!
Your perspective
might be a little
skewed...
Gimme a break! What
does this have to do
with stopping piracy!?
Trust me, you'll
see! I'll explain
everything shortly!
[grunt]
[growling]
ARGH!
[cheering and shouting]
(Narrator)
Dear me. Well, Lady
Tsunade, what exactly
was missing?
It just arrived,
as a matter of fact!
(Tsunade)
Make sure you all see
the new Naruto Movie!
(Narrator)
Ah, it was the movie poster!
Well, see you all at the
theaters, faithful viewers!
You've gotta be kidding
me! That was all pointless!?
(Neji)
Join us next time for
"Boom! The Shinobi
Fireworks Show,"
(Neji)
and "Bang! Tenten's
Acting Weird!"
(Tenten)
A fireworks show!?
I can't wait!
(Shikamaru)
With everyone off seeing
the display, I can get in
a good nap.
(Naruto)
I hear the ramen they
serve at those shows
is one of a kind!
(Lee)
Sakura's going to look
to pretty with her face
lit up by the sparklers!
(Tenten)
What about the actual
fireworks!?