When snow falls in the
Hidden Leaf Village, it
blankets everything in
pure white.
How are Lee and his
pals enjoying it?
Hey, that's not Lee...
Huh?!
Nice, they're surrounded!
Okay, let's get 'em!
Roger.
[gasps]
Huh?!
I must confirm
something. Is it
winter?
[sighing]
Because...
Shino, you idiot!
"Shino Loves Insects"
Wait... Hibernation?
Yes, that's right. Shino's
Parasitic Insects completely
stopped moving when the
weather turned cold.
Technically, they aren't
hibernating in the traditional
sense. They just don't want to
leave the warmth of my
body, becaus-
Okay, but why now?
It's frickin'
freezing, that's
why.
Yes, it's unseasonably
cold this year. Or as Kiba
so eloquently put it, it's
frickin' freezing.
Not having Shino's bugs
makes things tough. If
only there was another
species he could use...
Do you think you guys
could help us look
around for some.
Some insects? Sure,
no problem.
What?!
Hold on a second here,
we can't just drop
everything and-
Neji, please!
Right. Let's do it.
Hold on, you guys!
Honestly, I really don't
deal with bugs and insects
all that well.
I, uh... I don't like
them very much either.
So you're not alone
on that one. Sorry.
Hinata, to start saying that
now is very inconvenient.
That's because-
Suck it up, okay?!
Look, the type doesn't
matter, just find us some
bugs that are still moving!
Got it?
Yeah!
What?!
Because it would really
hurt my feelings.
Agh! So gross! We ended
up finding a ton of the
nasty little things!
I looked, but I could
only find this one.
Huh?!
Not good! That one's
trouble! Why? Because
that's a-
[screaming]
A stink bug!
Tenten, Hinata, calm down!
Pill bugs do not bite, stink,
or sting! They are harmless!
[screaming]
[screaming for help]
Don't any of you even
think about leaving!
Hinata, you should get
a medal for being on
this team.
Ehh...
It's no good.
Because...
[gasping]
They're too slow.
[sighing]
[groaning]
Forget about speed for
just a second. Surely you
could weaponize the stink
bugs, couldn't you?
Neji, I know you mean
well, but shut up!
[weeping]
Hey, then what
about this?
"The Love Bugs Movie".
Let us all count the
bug terms!
[chuckling]
It really bugs me how
selfish you two are!
How could you?
Enough already. Get off
your high horse! Now
come over here!
Don't touch me or
you'll really get
stung! I swear!
Who you trying to kid,
cry baby? You would not
hurt a fly, you little
tease!
You are trapped in our
web now, baby, and there
is no escape! Accept it,
toots.
No, get away!
Someone save me!
Freeze!
Hah!
Aghh!
Oh, Tenneth...
Hinata! I was so worried
you'd been stung by a
poisonous bug or something.
I'm sorry I worried
you, Father.
I can't...
Tell him...
I thought you'd been acting
strangely lately. That's
why I tailed you. How could
you?! What a filthy
little worm!
As your father, I am
putting my foot down.
Annoying mosquito! Just
looking at this poisonous
excuse for a human being
makes me as mad as a
hornet!
Dad, your such a meanie!
[gasp]
[screaming]
And just like that, the
little moth heads right
into the flame. So
predictable!
Our last little run-in
really ticked me off, but
now I'll get my revenge!
Don't worry, Daddy-o!
Let me handle these
guys!
Don't call me daddy
anything! We must
protect my daughter!
Those punks are knee-
high to a grasshopper!
We can take 'em!
[screaming]
Aw, man. They really
loused everything up.
Those punks...
Tenneth!
Hinata!
Maybe it's none of
my beeswax after all.
Hah! To each is
own, I guess.
Thank you for
understanding,
father.
The End.
[chuckle]
What in the heck are you
grinning about?! That
waste of two minutes
didn't solve a thing!
We don't even really
know where to look for
'em. We're not trained
bug hunters.
Good point. Let me
give you a brief
lecture, then.
You mean we're
still not done?!
During the winter, most
bugs stay under leaves,
under rocks, and under
tree bark. Observe.
He just found
Kakashi Sensei.
Huh?
Whoa! What's Kakashi doing
here? To answer that question,
we'll have to go back a little
bit. It happened like this...
You have to find me
within the time limit.
Everybody ready?
And that's pretty
much the whole story.
Kakashi Sensei?
Wait, I have got it!
That is not the real
Kakashi Sensei!
Huh? What are you
talking about, Lee?
Bugs live in tree bark,
right? And look at that
book. This is not
Kakashi...
It is a bookworm!
Ugh, that's so lame!
Ooh!
Oh, please. Don't be
impressed by such a
bad pun.
Prepare yourself!
Ah. That was
good. Because-
Awesome! That bookworm
that looks like Kakashi
rules!
There's no such
thing, okay?
Now we are finally
getting somewhere!
Alright, everyone!
Keep looking!
How many times do I have
to tell you? Kakashi
Sensei's not an insect.
I doubt there're any
more of your "insects"
out here-
Here is another.
Seriously?
You're kidding?!
What's Choji doing here,
you ask? Well, it happened
like this...
Hmm...Macarons from four
months ago. Should I eat
them? Or is it too risky?
[screaming]
What the heck happened?
Did I fall in a pit?
Well, it doesn't look
like I'll be getting out
of here anytime soon.
Don't wanna starve to
death! Guess I have
no choice!
No, no, no, they're
four months old. I
really shouldn't.
Aw, man! But they look
so good! Maybe just one...
No, no, no!
Agh! Stop it! No!
No, no, no...
But...
That's funny. I was just
thinking about him and
wondering where he'd been.
How's it going, Choji?!
Hold on a moment! This
hungry creature is not
Choji. It is actually...
A Stomach Bug!
[groaning]
It is not!
Enough puns!
I am sure there are
more nearby... Agh!
Gah! Agh! Under
this rock!
[groaning]
Captain Yamato, what're
you doing under there?!
Yes, what is Yamato
doing under there?
Actually, no one knows
what Yamato's deal is.
Despite what you think,
what you see before is not
Captain Yamato. It is another
type of bug.
A bug?
Yes, a bug.
Oh, great.
Let us take a moment
to interview him.
Captain Yamato, correct?
What is your favorite
type of food?
What do you like to
do in your free time?
You see?
See what, exactly?
Here I come!
Whoa!
They will collectively
make excellent replacements
for my usual bugs. Because-
Shino, this is
just too awesome!
Becaus-
They're the strongest
bugs I've ever seen!
Becau-
The bookworm, the stomach
bug, and the bug-bug!
Incredible!
Beca-
Are you seriously
going along with
this?
Be-
We should split up
and see how many more
bugs we can find.
Yeah!
I found a bedbug! Oh!
There's a grasshopper!
And a ladybug!
And so, Shino Aburame
assembled the greatest
insect army in history.
But this was merely the
prologue to him founding
the Hidden Bug Village,
and becoming its leader,
known far and wide as
the "Bug-Kage"!
Yeah, right. Like that
would ever happen.
[grunting]
In reality, everyone went
back home, and the team
had a craftily create a
warmer environment for
the original bugs to
continue working.
[sigh]
Keep it up, everyone.
Only 6,882 more bug
sweaters to go.
I can't take it!
Please, no more!
What seasonal activity
do women love more than
just about anything?
Hello and good morning!
It is time for another
early-morning trai-
Hold on...
Tenten is not here!
Apparently she's out
battling her fellow
females today.
Battling her
fellow female?
"Tenten fights a
Maiden's Battle!"
[chatter]
This year, I'm
winning it all!
Welcome to our store!
No pushing! No running!
Once again, no pushing!
No running!
Perfect rhythm!
Hah!
Please! No pushing,
no running! Just like
the announcement said!
Megaphones, radio
warnings, even whistles!
They're pulling out the
big guns as usual. But
this year, I'm prepared!
Foolish amateurs. They
only put cheap junk out
in the bins to lure in
suckers!
The real prizes are
always in the back!
[gasp]
Oh! Sorry about that!
Whoa!
Whoa! Move it
already!
Hey!
All of you are
here, too?
Looks like another
year of battling for
supremacy!
Don't think I've forgotten
last year's "Bamboo Pipe"
incident!
We may fight for the
same village, but today
it's every woman for
herself!
Um...sure...
I guess...
First thing is to get
that cute chain sickle
I saw during my recon...
There it is!
Huh?!
Ha! Ha! Heh!
You big cheater!
Here it is!
She's using
power moves?
It's "no holds barred"
time! Huh? Where'd it go?
Hey! What the?
Where'd it go?
Where is it?!
Byakugan!
Over there!
Huh!
I win this round!
I won't lose again!
[gasp]
The new classic ninja
hakama pants! They
debuted in the spring!
And they're sold out in
flamingo pink, too! What
a rare and lucky find!
Dibs on the pink one!
Hmm...
[grunting]
[gasp]
[screaming]
Tenten's fighting a
pro bargain hunter.
They mean business.
Looks like she's
gonna need a hand!
Huh?
[growling]
Wow, these have been
sold out forever!
Lucky me, I found a
rare collectible!
Y-yeah...
Too bad it's an
extra-large! Oh,
well!
Nice work, Ino! The
old Bargain Bluff
jutsu!
Yep, no sweat.
I, uh...
That is...
Thanks, guys.
I appreciate it.
I was thinking, maybe
we'd be better off
working together here.
That's true. A little
cooperation maybe
just what we need.
Being at each other's
throats will only hurt
us in the end.
This is truly
a war zone.
Strategy, weaponry, and
at times, emergency
measures. A female war
zone is a dangerous place
where only the most
merciless women come
out on top! Without
allies, you are doomed.
Special ops team Honey
and Boa, now in position.
Commanding unit Sunny
Spot, now in position.
Flower print wrist
armor spotted over
by mirror three!
Honey has visual
on that.
Boa, infiltrate
beneath the bin
and retrieve.
Yes, ma'am!
[ringing bell]
Hold on!
Hm?
Attention shoppers,
we are now holding a
special limited-time
ultra-discount sale!
Yes! The biggest
battle of the day
begins!
Change to mission
plan, "Iron Curtain!"
Iron Curtain!
Bargain Cliff!
The most dangerous foe
at this point in the game
is the bargain stealer.
Filthy cowards who snatch
your hard-earned clothes
the moment you leave
yourself open!
This is the perfect
formation! Optimally
balanced, offensively
and defensively.
We're gonna make
it this year!
[gasp]
Lady Tsunade?
Tenten? Is that you?
Huh?
I suggest you let go
of this one. Remember,
I am the Hokage.
Hokage or not, on the
floor of a bargain sale,
we're nothing but fellow
kunoichi and consumers.
I will not let go,
you got that?!
Excuse me?
Whoa, hold up! Deep
discount or not, this
is Lady Tsunade we're
dealing with.
There's just no
way we can beat
her.
Tenten...
She is a Legendary Sannin,
but things are different
this year than they have
been in the past.
[gasp]
Look, if we keep looking
together as a team, I
think we've got a chance.
Mmm...
Uh huh! So it's a fight
you're looking for, is it?
That's right!
Bring it on!
Now's our chance!
Yay!
Secret Technique:
Tablecloth Magic Trick!
An expert level move that
instantly identifies the
smoothest fabric in a
neatly folded stack.
To think a young girl
like her has mastered
it...
Hmph!
Huh?
Is that chainmail? It
looks pretty woven.
Wait! It's wool!
Organic wool? They'll
never pull that out!
No way!
Three, two, one, zero!
There's no way!
The roughest fabric
there is, grabbed like
it was nothing.
[grunting]
She moved the whole rack!
They cheat without batting
an eye. Adults are such
fearless opponents!
[yelling]
[screaming]
You see all that, girls?
We've been coming to sales
like this since before you
were born.
You never had
a chance!
Wait, before they
were born? We're
not that old...
Hm!
So many powerful
attacks. And to
make things worse.
They have such deep
pockets, too. There's
no hesitation in their
moves.
But we can't act as
they do. We think of
our wallets and pause
for that fraction of
a second. I hate to
admit it, but we're
outclassed.
Well, then...
Huh?
We need to fight on
a field where money
doesn't matter.
You game? Are you
still with me, ladies?!
Yes, of course
we are!
At this point we all
share the same fate.
Count us in!
Yes, Tenten. We're
with you to the end!
Hm...
I'll admit you've
completely dominated
us so far today.
But there's still
one final battle
yet to be fought.
The most dangerous
and difficult one
of them all.
You don't mean...
We challenge you to
the forbidden "Grab
Bag Throwdown!"
Are you trying to
get yourselves
killed!
Huh, what was that?
You're not scared,
are you, Lady Tsunade?
[growling]
Fine then! We accept!
Prepare yourselves!
Whew, now I've
done it.
Sorry about that. I know
that grab-bags are the
equivalent of land mines
waiting to blow.
But it was the only thing
I could think of going on
here today where we at
least have a chance
at beating the adults.
Don't be silly, Tenten.
It's a great plan. We
just need to win.
Yeah, she's right!
Let's do it!
We'll beat them, and
return to the village
arm in arm, okay?
Hm! Yeah!
Considering the season,
the heavy ones will be
coats. High value targets,
but the wrong choice
will prove fatal.
The uneven weight suggests
multiple items. That does
spread out the risk, but...
We could take a chance...
And pick a light one
hoping that it's something
really valuable!
They're using their
grownup finances to
win with sheer numbers?
We won't know for
sure until we open
these suckers up!
Now let the battle begin!
Go!
What in the world?!
What is this
supposed to be?
How in the heck do
you even wear this
thing?
O...kay...
[screaming]
Let's take a look to
see what's in this one!
[screaming]
Ugh!
Aghh!
Down to the last
two grab bags.
Bring it on!
A 10 pack of
Guy Suits?!
Lee suits?!
Unitards?! Are
you kidding me?!
It was nothing
but junk...
Of course, in anime, no
one ever changes their
clothes. So it doesn't
really matter anyway.
Never fear! Here
comes the calvary!
Yahh!
Let me help!
Where is the
battle?!
How'd I get
talked into
this?
The next episode is, "17 Nights
of Staying out of Sight" and
"Cleaning the Bathroom
Cleanses the Soul."
Come to think of it,
you're 17, aren't you,
Lee? Huh. You really
don't look it...
Yes, indeed! And I will
be 17 next year and the
year after that, as well!
Such is the life of
an anime character.
You too, right,
Tenten?
Eh, yeah, sure. I'm
eternally 17, too.
Boy, they really can do
some crazy things with
the settings, huh?