(Narrator)
Autumn is finally
here! One season ends,
and another begins!
(Narrator)
And you know what
else begins..?
Sports!
-A sports tournament?
That's right! A ball
game tourney is being
held this Sunday!
I am burning with
anticipation!!!
The ball game tournament
and sports meet are the
two big events that take
place in the fall!
Is this tournament
you're talking about
really that big?
And could you take your
anticipation flame down
a notch? It's burning
out of control!
There are all kinds
of ball games, though.
Which one is it?
Oh... that is right.
Which game is the
tournament for?
[laughter] "Which
game," you ask?
It's for Dodgeball!
[groans]
"The Green Flame,
Dodge Lee!"
I see. Dodgeball,
huh?
What's wrong, Lee? You
Don't sound excited
about it anymore.
Don't you like it?
Well, it is not
that I do not
like it, but...
...when I think
of dodgeball...
So, tell me! How
far are you into
Narutimate?
I just made it
to the cave!
Yeah? I'm at
the wind tower.
Woah! Really?
I swear, boys are
just so completely
childish...
HOnestly, the game
simply seems kind
of childish to me.
I hate to break it to
you, but, it's not the
dodgeball that's childish,
it's the boys.
Don't be such
a softie!
You're even softer
than these cream-
covered dorayaki!
Stop eating that nasty
crap! Your blood sugar
will go through the roof!
Listen to me, Lee!
Dodgeball... is a
serious game that tests
the most fundamental
ninja skills!
(Lee)
Really? Are
you sure?
(Guy)
Clearly you don't
see it that way.
Fine. I'll show you.
Right! A little
exhibition match
should help you
understand...
Behold! The depth
of dodgeball!
I just do not get
it, Guy Sensei.
For a ninja, handling
a large object like a
dodgeball is nothing!
Especially compared
to the skill needed
to handle a kunai!
(Guy)
Come on, Lee!
Throw it!
Oh! Alright!
Woooahhh! Oof!
GAH! My apologies!
I know that face
hits do not count!
[sobbing]
(Lee)
Um, uh... Guy
Sensei..?
(Tenten)
Poor thing!
Huh!?
What's wrong
with you!? That
was too rough!
What!?
This is training! Take
it easy, would you?
Not this again!
Ah! It was an
accident! I swear!
I did not mean to
hit him in the--
GOTCHA!
See that?
In dodgeball, if you
let your guard down,
even for a second,
you get hurt.
The "dodgeball"
part was finished
way before he
got hurt...
(Guy)
A ninja must always
be sure to secure
his own safety...
...and endure until
his chance to strike
presents itself.
That is basic
ninja conduct.
What a fearsome
game..!
I never knew
dodgeball was
so complex!
How can I gain the
patience to endure
like that!? Please
teach me!
Visualize it, Lee...
See yourself...
dodging the ball...
Okay! I will
try it!
That's the spirit!
Visualize!
(Shizune)
It looks like our fall
dodgeball tournament
is finally underway!
Shizune here, as your
play-by-play announcer,
with Lady Tsunade on
color commentary!
Hello!
(Shizune)
Our first match pits
Team Guy against Team
Ebisu.
Alright! You're going
down, Bushy Brow!
Bring it on,
Konohamaru!
[chuckle]
Who do you give
this match to,
Lady Tsunade?
Five silver on
Team Ebisu!
You're betting
on this..!?
[whistle blow]
Here goes!
Visualize, Lee!
Visualize... Yes.
I will undulate like
a gentle wave and
gracefully dodge...
[happy sigh]
What the heck!? Why
are you relaxing!?
The ball's coming
right for you!
Lee!
Snap out of it!
You have to focus!
[nauseous groan]
Hey! What's with
all the nausea!?
I have come down
with imaginary
morning sickness...
I think you mean
imaginary seasickness!
It's time for round 2,
Bushy Brow! Get ready!
I will just have
to... use the...
drunken fist...
I see right through
your clever ruse!
Sexy Jutsu!
[excited scream]
Owww!
(Shizune)
And Lee is out!
What!? How can you
be such an idiot!?
(Neji)
I'll get them!
Huh?
Neji!
Time for Gentle Fist!
Eight Trigrams!
Sixy-Four Palm!
Ow ow ow ow ow!
Nice one, Neji!
We are so finished...
(Shizune)
Team Guy wins!
[crowd cheering]
Things weren't looking
so good for Team Guy when
Lee was eliminated early
on in the match...
But they managed to
earn themselves a
victory thanks to
Neji's dedication!
What are your thoughts
on the outcome, Lady
Tsunade?
Just take it,
you thief!
And with that,
we're on to
the semi-finals!
(Shizune)
Team Kurenai!
Shino starts off
right with a jutsu!
It looks like the
ball has suddenly
vanished!
Remember, Lee,
visualize...
Ahhhh, uhhh,
Ooof!
(Shizune)
And just like that,
Lee is out again!
Hiyyya!
Eight Trigrams
Palm Rotation!
(Shizune)
Again, the opposing
team is out in one
fell swoop!
We're not done!
Severe Leaf Hurricanes!
(Shizune)
There's no need
to blow away
the spectators!
(Shizune)
Team Guy comes from
behind for another win!
Ugh! I'll win
next time!
With that, it's
time for the finals!
[weep]
(Shizune)
It's team Guy vs.
Team Kakashi for
the championship!
You guys are so going
down, Bushy Brow!
I have been nothing
but dead weight to
the team. I am
totally useless...
Don't worry...
Just concentrate.
Visualize, and you
can do it, okay?
You keep telling
me that, but...
The match is
about to begin!
Which way are you
leaning on this,
Lady Tsunade?
Number 8 in
the fifth...
You're betting on
horses now!? Take
those off an pay
attention!
Special Big League
Rasengan, Version One!
Woah, what the heck!?
[screams]
(Shizune)
And Tenten is
eliminated! Oh!
Tenten!
(Naruto)
I'm not done yet!
The same move
won't work twice!
Byakugan!
(Shizune)
What a maneuver! He's
mixed the ball in with
his Rasengan!
Where's the ball!?
Ah!
What an ingenious
combination!
Naruto's Rasengan's
were just a distraction!
(Shizune)
Team Guy is down
to just Lee and Guy.
(Shizune)
Team Kakashi is
the real deal!
(Shizune)
It looks like Lee
is in serious trouble!
(Guy)
Don't give up, Lee!
Oh!
Visualize it. Come on,
you can do it! Visualize!
Guy Sensei...
Visualize...
I'm being persistent, huh?
But I'll keep being
bossy and persistent!
This is just like...
Oh, persist?!
Ah! That is it!
Get ready, Bushy
Brow! Big League
Rasengan!
[hiccup]
The Drunken Fist?
But why? It didn't
work last time!
(Guy)
Think again!
-Huh?
That's no ordinary
Drunken Fist. Lee!
(Guy)
Have you finally
done it!?
Hm!
(Guy)
One more round, Rock!
"One more round,"
huh? Come on, boss.
Let us go.
Chief Guy sure
is persistent...
It is always the same:
The bar by the station,
then another round at
karaoke...
...and finally,
a big bowl of
ramen. I have to
escape...
Oh yeah! Party
time! We're going
all night!
Uh, boss?
Huh?
Sorry, I just... You
know, I got that
thing... and I gotta
get home. Understand?
Huh? [hiccup]
Wife's waitin'
for ya, huh?
I get it. Run
along then.
Take care of
yourself!
Yes, sir!
(Shizune)
He ducked it! He ducked
it like a man ducking
a persistent boss!
What!? That kind of
ducking works here!?
That's it, Lee!
Just keep on ducking!
Come on! Is this
really the right
lesson to learn!?
Man! What an
effective way
to dodge!
I have got that thing!
This makes no
sense at all!
Why do you have
to be a business
man to be an
expert dodger!?
Yes! Now for the
counterattack!
Be my guest!
Thanks, I
appreciate it!
Hm! Balding Salaryman
Whirlwind!
[screaming]
Crap! We lost!
(Shizune)
Team Guy takes it
with another
comeback victory!
Nice job, Lee!
I finally understand!
Dodgeball is not just
some silly sport
intended for kids!
It is an adult-
oriented game
of skill!
I don't think you
understand what
any of that means.
Idiot... Idiot...
(Narrator)
Fall sports are best
enjoyed together as
a family....
(Narrator)
Nobody's perfect. Even the
most respected experts can
be wrong from time to time.
(Narrator)
It just happens. But
what about this guy?
(Orochimaru)
[shouting]
Are you alright,
Lord Orochimaru?
My ingenious plan
failed again!
I dressed as
an old man for
"Respect Your
Elders" day...
I nursed an injured
sparrow back to health
and got a wicker rice
basket as gratitude.
I planned on using
it to catch those
meddling Leaf kids
in a trap...
But it seems I got
the date wrong.
"Respect Your Elders"
week was last week!
Those punks. They
couldn't have cared
less about a
friendly old man!
[sigh] Don't
kid yourself.
I think the problem is
much more fundamental
than just getting
the date wrong.
Shut your mouth!
I don't need to be
lectured by someone
obviously weaker
than me!
Well if I may
be frank...
With the way you
constantly fail, I'd
say that you're the
"obviously weaker" one.
You didn't say that!
Tell me you didn't
just say that!
What exactly do you
think you do better,
you petulant pinhead!?
P-.. Pin...
head..?
Who are you
calling a
pinhead!?
That does it! I'll
show you exactly how
capable I am, you jerk!
[growling]
"The Yes-Man Says 'No!'"
Well, that's the way
I see it, anyway.
Oh! Look over there!
Oh, pose-able
figure... You're
my only friend!
Is that not
Orochimaru's
underling?
Yeah, no doubt
about it!
The little traitor
must be here to
attack the Leaf again!
Hey! What are
you doing here?!
Oh... it's
you guys...
I was just...
wasting time...
-Huh?
That seems odd.
Is he okay?
Lee, this man's
our enemy! We
should stay on
guard!
Yes, of course. But
seeing him in such a
depressed state has
me a bit worried.
Hey, if you have
something on your
mind, you can talk
to us about it.
Oh, yes?
(Lee / Neji / Tenten)
You cut ties with
Orochimaru...!?
Yes, that's right. I
just don't have the
heart to follow that
path anymore...
The way he uses his
powers as a shinobi
for such evil purposes?
It's just plain wrong!
So, wait, that would
be the reason you
left and ran away?
Yes, and it got
me thinking...
Now that I'm free,
would you let me
join your group?
What!?
No way! Are
you serious?!
All this time I've
done nothing but
work for him..!
Now that I don't, I
have no idea where
to go!
Look, I'm a changed
man! I just want the
chance to live an
honest life... Please!
Even if that's
true, we really...
I understand the
concern, but I do
feel for him. If he
has really changed?
[chuckle]
They're such suckers
for sob-stories!
I join their group, get
them to relax... and
then I slaughter them!
...That's the plan!
(Narrator)
Ah-ha! So that's
what's going on!
I'll show Lord Orochimaru
that I'm more powerful
than him..!
...more powerful than
he ever dreamed of!
(Neji)
Hold it!
Huh?
Let's not forget,
this guy used to
be a double agent-
using every waking
moment to work
against the Leaf!
No matter what he
says, I don't think
we can trust him!
Very well...
I understand your
concern and suspicion.
But I swear,
I've changed!
I'm not the man
I once was..!
And I'll prove
it to you!
What do you think
about that..?
Wow! Take a look
at you! How about
that?
You're acting just like
some sort of bitter
ex-boyfriend or something!
Nothing will change if
we keep doubting him!
If he is willing to
go that far, we should
give him a chance.
Yeah? Well, if
you say so, Lee.
I've got a bad
feeling about
this, but I'll
go along.
Thank you!
They're such a
trusting bunch!
How pathetic...
Now to make them
lower their guard...
On to the next step!
If you want to join
our circle, you have
to pass the test!
Huh? Test?
"Rock Lee Ninja Pal
Application Test"
Wait, what's
going on, here!?
I said I wanted to
join their team...
What am I doing in
an exam room...?!
Attention! The
test is about
to begin!
As you can see,
we've got a lot
of applicants this
time around...
But despite the
number interested,
only one of you can
become our ninja pal!
Good luck! Do
your best, everyone!
This is more like
some sort of weird
audition...
Everyone here today is
very excited! They all
assumed that we would be
done after 2 seasons.
But when they heard we
were renewed for a 3rd...
...they rushed in to
try and ride our coattails
for their own bit of fame,
fortune, and screen time!
I'm not excited
about that stuff!
Don't lump me in
with this bunch
of one-offs!
Nice one! You completely
destroyed the fourth wall.
And why would any of
these guest characters
even know that sort
of thing...?
Anyway, I want to see
just how determined
everyone is! Let me
hear you!
[cheering]
Whatever! I'll win
no matter what
the cost..!
Okay! Would the next 5
applicants please make
their way to the
interview room?
I'm up...
Reporting for testing!
What's Lord
Orochimaru
doing here!?
So, you're here,
too, Kabuto...
I see- That's
how it is...!
I deduced your
transparent plan
right away...
I'd expect nothing
less, Lord Orochimaru.
You had the same idea.
We're both trying to join
them, gain their trust,
and then strike when
they least expect it, yes?
It looks like we
have ourselves a
challenge....
Only one of us can
win this contest.
And that one of us
is going to be ME!
So, first off, I
would like you to tell
us why you would like
to join the firm.
Firm!? What is this,
a law office...!?
Hold it, if I'm going
to be accepted, I have
to play along with
their little games...
First, Mr. Kabuto
Yakushi.
Right. Well, I feel I've
reached my full potential
here working as part of
this organization...
What textbook is
that response from?
You could've just said,
"What is this, a law
office!?" Such a shame
to miss a good punchline.
Besides, we already
have a top-tier straight
man in our firm!
Why do you keep
saying, "Firm!?"
Wait, was that
straight man you were
talking about me!?
Case and point!
Oh, crap! So they
wanted me to play
along on a deeper
level!?
(Lee)
Next applicant,
please...
Well, I... I...
Uh...
What's this!? He's
too nervous to answer?!
Good. Lord
Orochimaru will
lose points for
that!
I... I mean...
[big screaming yell]
[more screaming]
And that perfectly
describes how badly
I want to work here.
What a ridiculous
performance!
Expressing your desire
like that will get
you nowhere!
Wow! I really felt your
desire to work here!
Are you freaking
kidding me!?
Not only do I see just
how much you want to be
here, but that made for a
great comedic setup, too!
Really amazing work!
I'm awarding extra
points for that!
The amount of stupidity
you two are capable of
is shocking...
Next, I would like for
each of you to tell us
a tale about your skills!
I, for one, have a
lot of experience
with medical jutsu!
That's a short
tale. My tai's
a bit longer!
My goodness! That
is quite a tale,
indeed! Well done!
I see that you're
good with simple
puns, too.
More extra points
for you....
Darn it all! I
shouldn't have
given the straight
answer!
Morons! Every last
one of your! Morons!
And now for the
elevator pitch.
This is your last
chance to really
make an impact.
Best of luck!
Make an impact..?
What should I say?
I'll go first,
if you don't mind.
What!?
I win, Kabuto.
This story will have
such a huge impact,
they'll have no choice
but to go with me!
Get a load of
this,loser!
I'm not going to die!
This won't kill me
because, I love yo--
Oh my goodness! What
a heartwarming story!
He wanted to prove that
the love he felt for her
would protect him even
from death itself!
But in the end, he
was hit by a truck,
and... wait!
That's the wrong kind
of impact, you idiot!
Wow! That was great!
Huh?
First you played along,
then nailed the punchline!
It was amazing!
Even our very own
punchline wizard
Tenten isn't good enough
to pull a move like that!
What do you mean,
"punchline wizard?!"
And with that, you
just passed with a
perfect score!
Congratulations!
Agreed! You pass!
Three points for
Hara Taira!
Why the heck
are they betting!?
I... I passed?
Really?
Heh, I admit
defeat.
Lord Orochimaru...
Kabuto, before
when I said that
you were obviously
weaker than me...
I was bluffing.
Huh?
I wanted to force
you to step out
of my shadow.
To decide things on
your own terms! To
be all you can!
You're a very strong
man, Kabuto. Much
stronger than me...
I don't know what
to say...
Farewell, Kabuto.
I'm sorry! I had
no idea, but I
understand now!
You were just trying to
help me grow! You have
a much bigger heart than
I could ever hope to have!
I know this is
sudden, but I'm quitting
as your new pal!
This was all part
of my plan.
I was going to
infiltrate your group,
gain your trust, and
take you all out!
But I am going to
beat you without any
of that underhanded
trickery!
[evil laughter]
You revealed your
true self, Kabuto!
Even if you hadn't
quit, you still lose!
Serves you right, you
traitorous buffoon!
You still think you're
better than me, do you?
[evil laughter]
Grrr... Why you
little..!
You were trying to so
the exact same thing!
I could tell right
away! You're not
fooling anybody!
No fair! Outing
me is against the
rules, you jerk!
This is what makes
you a petulant pinhead!
That again!?
Seriously!?
I'm not a pinhead
you reptilian goon!
I don't know how
I've put up with
you for so long!
(Orochimaru)
Shut up, you moody brat!
(Kabuto)
What was that!?
[screaming]
(Narrator)
And the total number
who passed was....
(Narrator)
...Zero!
Womp womp...
(Tenten)
On the next episode,
join us for "My First
Five-Star Sushi!"
(Tenten)
And, "Friendship,
Effort, and Victory!"
(Lee)
Five-star sushi, huh?
So, if it is not on a
conveyor belt, do we just
spin around instead?
(Tenten)
Seriously!? Of
course not!
(Tenten)
Only mature adults eat
at sushi places like that.
(Lee)
Right right! I
understand now!
(Lee)
So I should order
quid, and then change
my order to sea urchin-
(Lee)
and then eat the whole thing,
and then complain about the
taste when I am done!
(Lee)
Excellent plan, right?
(Tenten)
You're not supposed to
abuse your power as a
customer like that!