(Narrator)
Dearest viewers, do you
believe in miracles?
(Neji / Tenten / Lee)
WHAT!?
You seriously hit the
jackpot in the lottery!?
[chuckle] Yep, it
looks like ol' Lady
Luck has finally revised
her poor opinion of me!
And now I've decided to reward
you 3 for training so hard day
in and day out-- by treating
you to whatever you want!
What'll it be!?
Really!? Anything?
Let's see... what
should we ask for?
Oh!
I want to go out to
eat sushi, but sit at
the bar instead of at
a table!
Huh?
Eating sushi at the
bar... that is the
first big step to
becoming an adult!
"My First Five-Star Sushi"
(Lee)
The sushi bar...
A place where countless men have
taken their families and
girlfriends out for what they
think will be a pleasant meal...
...only to find a
battlefield where the
line between life and
death is razor thin!
(Tenten)
What kind of narration is
that? It's way too dramatic.
(Tenten)
It's like some role-
playing game!
(Lee)
But with Lady Tsunade
treating us, we will be
(Lee)
able to circumvent the
danger and reach our
sushi unharmed!
Tomorrow the 3 of
us will get to stuff
ourselves silly! Yahoo!
Uh...
Huh? Oh, hey! What's
up, Bushy Brow?
Hi, Sakura! Boy,
do we have news
for you!
Idiot...! Idiot...!
(Narrator)
But what about the
beneficiary of
today's windfall?
[horrified groan]
[happy humming]
[crying] I can't
believe that I had
the wrong number!
How stupid!
This isn't supposed
to be a gag anime!
(Narrator)
Um, that's exactly
what it is..!
And I promised those
three that I'd taken
them out to eat! What
am I gonna do..!?
I cannot believe
that you had the
wrong number! How
stupid!
And what a hackneyed
plot device, too!
That's so lame!
Some Hokage you
turned out to be!
I'll tarnish the
title of Hokage!
[gasp] Wait!
It would be better if
we brought everyone
along and made a party
out of it!
Conveyor belt Sushi!
Who's with me!?
I think I can
afford that kind
of place...
(Lee)
Lady Tsunade!
Arghhh!!
We wanted to talk to
you about going to eat
at the sushi restaurant!
Oh, right!
Excellent
timing!
It would be better
if we brought everyone
along and made a party
out of it!
Yes! Indeed!
So I invited
Naruto's group!
[horrified gasp]
Just think! All of
us sitting together
at the bar...
Wahoo! It it time for
the party to begin!
Yeah!!!
But I... Uh...
[screaming]
Idiot..! Idiot..!
[grunts]
Idiot! A brainless
idiot! That's what
I am!
The prior Hokage
must be rolling in
their graves..!
Lady Tsunade..?
Are you alright?
Huh?
(Guy)
I see... that
is difficult...
I promised them that
I'd take them out to
ear, so I can't back
out of it now!
I need to think of a way to
trick th em into not wanting
to go without doing any more
damage to my reputation!
Aren't they a little
young to be sitting
at the bar, anyway?
Maybe you can
use that?
Yes! That's it,
Lady Tsunade!
I know how to preserve
your honor as Hokage
and to make them forget
all about eating sushi
at a five-star restaurant
all at once!
You can just leave
everything to
Kakashi and me!
Huh? And me?
(Narrator)
The day of the dinner...
[excited chattering]
Ugh, some help Guy
turned out to be.
He's completely
unreliable!
We're still heading
to the restaurant!
(Guy)
Hold it!
Huh?
We both heard that all
of you are planning on
stuffing yourselves at some
fancy-schmancy sushi bar.
Uh... yes?
Why? What
about it?
All of you are too
young to sit at
the bar, that's what!
Way too young!
You hear!?
(Guy)
During the Leaf's economic
bubble, all the young ninja
were living it up!
...eating fancy sushi
at the bar...
But then the bubble burst,
and their spendthrift ways
caught up with them, leaving
them penniless!
(Kakashi)
Wait, what economic
bubble are you
talking about..?
As far as I can
see, the only
bubbles here are
in your brain...
(Guy)
The sushi bar is a
war zone that swallows
young ninja whole!
(Kakashi)
Speaking of swallow, I
can't believe you can
swallow that story!
LIsten! When you guys grow up
a little bit more, and become
strong-willed ninja who aren't
so easily swayed by temptation-
...then, and only
then, may you all
sit at the sushi bar!
Well, Guy may be
exaggerating a bit,
but I have to admit,
he does have a point.
Not you, too,
Kakashi Sensei!
Perhaps they are right
and we are too young
to eat at the bar...
But still! Our strong will
to eat loads and loads of
sushi is absolutely unshakable!
Mhm!
Oh? Really? Let's
put your will to
the test, then!
What do you
mean "test?"
Alright, everyone,
listen up!
You're about to
undergo the most
grueling of tests:
Sit at the bar,
order what you want,
eat, and leave.
Do you really think
you can handle it?
(Kakashi)
If you succeed, then
we'll acknowledge you
as full-fledged ninja.
Let me get this straight,
all we have to do is sit
at the bar, order, and eat?
That's right!
Oh, please! This'll
be a cakewalk!
Yes! I am certain
all of us will pass!
[scheming chuckle]
Alright, I'll
go first.
I'm going to eat
some of that salmon
roe no matter what!
(Guy)
Welcome!
[gasp] W-what,
what is this?
You're late, Haruno.
Come have a seat.
Oh, right.
What'll it be?
Let's see... Squid,
octopus, and gizzard
shad.
The same for
you, miss?
Uh.
Go ahead.
Uh, yeah sure.
Here's your squid,
octopus, and gizzard shad.
Oh, I... uh...
[buzzer sound]
HUH!??
[screaming]
Sakura noooo!
I understand.
She broke a social taboo, that a
young employee should never
order something so expensive
when her boss is treating her.
So this is what
adults go through...
If your spirit wavers
even a little, then you
miss your chance to eat
what you really want?
Do you really think
that's what it means
to have a strong will!?
At least now we
know what to expect.
And that means I'm
going on the offensive!
Ah, welcome!
But you're still
late, Konohamaru.
Get me salmon roe!
Here.
Mine, mine mine!
[screaming]
Too much wasabi!!!
That poor fool. He
forgot to tell them
to hold the wasabi.
Failing to handle
wasabi is a fatal
weakness...
No, us getting pulled into
these ridiculous skits over
and over again is the real
fatal weakness!
Alright! I've got a
sure-fire plan to
get some fatty tuna!
Byakugan!
Nice one! Now he can
see if there is any
wasabi inside his sushi!
Or, he could just ask them
to hold the wasabi...
Hey old man,
I'll have...
What do I want?
[horrified gasp]
Sea urchin, shrimp,
your fattiest tuna,
and a caterpillar roll.
And what about
you, Neji honey?
What!? That's the
most expensive stuff
on the menu!
It'll cost me...
So, what'll
it be, sir?
Uh, give me...
Yes..?
A cucumber roll.
[screaming]
[buzzer sound]
When your girlfriend
orders an expensive meal,
you obsess over the cost!
And as a result, you end
up ordering something
that's inexpensive in order
to balance out what she bought.
Bushier Brow Sensei
knows scary tactics!
Not as scary as Neji gullibly
falling for Guy Sensei
pretending to be his girlfriend!
That's it! I'm
going to go in next.
I'm a girl, so money will
be no object whatsoever!
Hello there! Some
flounder, please.
(Kakashi)
Flounder, comin' up!
Mommy! I wanna try
flounder! Get some
for me right now,
mommy!
Forget it! Kids eat
kid's sushi, so have
an egg roll or a
salad or something!
(Kakashi)
One flounder...
Huh!?
Uh, what do
you want?
I feel really bad
eating this in
front of him!
[buzzer sound]
[screaming]
I had no idea that
a sushi bar is so
riddled with
unforeseen traps!
Set all the traps
you want..!
If every single seat
at the bar is taken,
then that doesn't matter!
Okay, pops, one tuna!
[shouting]
-That's how you counterpunch!
Wow! That was a
flawless counterpunch!
He just backed them
into a corner so
they had no choice!
There's only one
left now...
Are you finally beginning
to see that you're
simply not yet ready
to sit down at the bar!?
Maybe they are right,
after all. Maybe it
is too soon for us.
Conveyor belt sushi
is plenty for you
right now.
Conveyor belt sushi...
revolves! That is it!
Well, Lee? What's
it going to be?
Alright. I would
like lean tuna please,
Ahhhhhh!
Great Leaf Hurricane!
What's... he doing!?
He's moving just like...
...A sushi conveyor
belt rotating around
the counter!
Yes! I need to approach
this like I'd approach
a conveyor belt sushi
restaurant!
This is the only way
to stop my wavering and
impose the strength of
my will!
[chomp]
"Thank you, conveyor
belt sushi!"
"Farewell sushi bar!"
What just happened!?
Why is this up here?!
He isn't saying
goodbye at all!
Well, it looks like
they got one past
us, doesn't it?
Yep, we lost
this one.
Not quite. I learned
something when I used
the Great Leaf
Hurricane just now.
I am more confidents
being at a conveyor
belt sushi restaurant!
So I am going to
hold off on sitting
at the sushi bar until
I am truly an adult!
Lee...
Listen, if you still
want to go, I'd be
happy to treat all
of you to that!
Yeah! Alright!!!
(Narrator)
And so, Lee and his
pals swore they'd make
it to the bar someday.
But... unfortunately
for Tsunade, their
appetites more than made
up for the price difference.
Why does this
happen to me?
(Narrator)
It's the end of
another beautiful
autumn afternoon.
Guy Sensei really put
us through the wringer
today with those exercises.
What do you guys
want to do now?
I do not know.
Maybe enjoy the cool
breeze and relax with
a good book?
There's no breeze on
earth that's cool enough
to make that relaxing!!
Not even in the
Arctic Circle!
I mean, come on, you
don't have to act like
Guy Sensei when you're
reading a book too, ya know!
You do not understand,
Tenten! Guy Sensei is
my hero!
I want to be like
him as fast as I can!
Hey, look there.
Iruka Sensei!
It has been a while!
Oh, it's you
three, huh...
Huh?
"Friendship, Effort,
and victory!"
(Neji / Tenten / Lee)
You can't teach!?
Yeah. Once a week,
in addition to my usual
teaching duties, I
teach the lower grades.
(Iruka)
Unfortunately, most of
those kids are very spoiled.
They refuse to listen
to a word I say...
And they have zero
interest in trying
to work together...
If I scold them, they
just start crying!
But worst of all, I
have to deal with
their parents.
Enough!
Oh, I see!
They are what they
call "intimidator
parents," is that right?
No, you mean
"helicopter parents."
And there's going to
be an open house
coming up soon...
If I lose control of those
kids during that, then I'm
gonna get into big trouble.
But I can't yell at
them, or I'll upset
their moms.
Just thinking about the
whole thing gives me a
headache...
Yes, I understand.
I say, we come in like
we did last time--
--and give them a hot-blooded
lesson in friendship, effort,
and exactly what it takes to
achieve victory!
(Tenten)
The only thing that looks
like a lesson in, is a
Shonene Jump manga!
Their whole life, those
kids have been raised
believing that they can do
whatever they please.
They couldn't care less
about ideas like friendship
and effort...
and the only work you
used that they'd respond
to is "victory."
Thanks anyway...
[sigh] What am I
going to do...?
Wow, they really
don't care about
friendship or effort?
You wouldn't get
along with them
very well, Lee.
Well, maybe not those
parts, but I do like
victory like they do!
That's it!
Victory!
Huh?
Listen, the kids in his
class already like the
idea of winning, right?
Well then, we just need to use
that as the foundation for
teaching them all about the joys
of teamwork and effort!
Yes, I follow your logic,
but how do we go about
putting it into practice?
Well... uh...
You think we should
go ask Guy Sensei?
Oh?
Yes, Guy Sensei!
We can use Guy Sensei!
(Narrator)
Then, on the day
of the open house...
Anyway, as I was
saying... this...
[defeated sigh]
[classroom chatter]
Just what is
going on here?
This lesson isn't
challenging my smart
little sweet pea,
that's for sure!
I'm going to
the school board!
[sigh]
This is awful...
[scream]
Huh?
What's wrong!?
Iruka Sensei!
Some bad guys are
attacking us!
What? Some
bad guys?
Everyone just
stay calm!
Wha?
Hah hah hah
haaaah!
That's right! Us
bad guy underlings
are here...
And we're gonna steal
every last one of
your lunches from
you!
We may just be
underlings, but
don't try to
stop us...
What a drag...
Wait a second...
Sensei, do something
about these men!
Yes! You have to
protect my little
sweet pea!
Or else I'm going to
the school board!
Now, just hold on!
(Lee)
ENOUGH!
[gasps]
Just leave this situation
in our capable hands!
The Leaf Strawman
Heros will handle it!
And who're the Leaf
Strawman Heros
supposed to be..?
(Thought Narration)
I'll explain...
The Leaf Strawman Heros are an
elite squadron of warriors
Who teach children the value of
friendship and effort in their
quest for justice and victory!
Why am I narrating this?
What are you
guys doing?!
(Thought Narration)
I'll explain...
Bushy Brow asked us to come help
him put on a skit about heros to
teach your class the value of
effort and friendship.
Why do you have
to put on a hero
show skit to teach
them that?
(Thought Narration)
I'll explain...
Listen, all of you
just stop narrating,
alright!?
We can use Guy Sensei!
(Neji / Tenten)
Guy Sensei!?
We can use him as
our example and
become true heros
exactly like him!
(Lee)
It is an immutable
fact that children
look up to heros!
If we become heros and
demonstrate friendship and
effort, they will learn to
appreciate them for sure!
So please, just leave
this to us, Iruka Sensei.
Uh... Yeah okay.
Good luck, Lee.
Now! Everyone,
transform!
Show them the awesome
power of our perfectly
synchronized teamwork!
-Right!
-Switch!
-Go!
-Change!
None of you are
in synch at all!
-Now! Switch modes!
-Right! Got it!
-Begin Change!
-Yeah! Transform!
You're gonna have to
try harder than that
to get into synch!
Hiyah!
Red Hero, go!
Red Hero, ready
for action!
Red Hero! All
powered up!
-On the scene!
The one time you
synch up, and it's
just the color!?
All of us agreed
that I get to be red.
No way! I get
to be red!
Forget it! I
wanna do it!
It doesn't matter what
color you guys are,
just get on with it,
already, would you!?
(Neji)
Hey Lee...
Huh?
Why do I have to
be the one in pink?
Oh, why not, Neji?
Because it's weird,
and not a good look
for me!
Look, no one cares!
You can change, but
this is the only
spare costume we have.
Hmm....
Red Hero ready!
Oh, come on!
You're all red?!
I guess each of them
wanted to be the leader.
They've just got
too much freedom!
(Thought Narration)
I'll explain...
The Strawman Heros are
spoiled warriors who
obtained their powers without
any trials or hardships.
What kind of
backstory is that!?
This was supposed
to be about effort
and friendship!
Oh! This is
bad news!
Oh, finally! We're
getting back on
track now.
There is no Yellow
Hero on our team!
Not this again!
You know, Yellow Heros
always love curry.
Right, Bushy Brow?
No way! I am
going to be
the red one!
Good grief.
Alright, fine.
Listen up! Is there
anyone here who really
likes to eat curry?
Are you just holding
open auditions to
join the team!?
Uh... I like it!
Choji! You're supposed
to be the bad guy!
We're on the scene!
The enemy can't
change sides like
that!
(Thought Narration)
I'll explain...
You see, the Strawman Heros
are happy to accept random
people as their friend.
But that totally cheapens
the idea that you built a
strong friendship between
all of you!
This is more of
a drag every second.
[fearful murmurs]
Do not be afraid!
The Strawman Heros will
protect every last one
of you without fail!
Just leave
it to us!
The only one that
you're protecting
right now is Sakura!
Quickly! We gotta
defend the whole
class from that
bad guy!
Then stop hiding
under the desk and
get to work!
We have to get serious!
They won't learn anything
about effort or friendship
at this rate...
Do not worry!
If we fight back with teamwork
and win, the kids are sure to
understand the value of
friendship and effort.
[chuckle]
You will not be
able to escape
from us now!
(Tenten)
Now you seem like
you're the bad guys!
Go get em!
Strawman Heroes!
Kick! Hiyah!
Man... what
a drag...
That's it!?
You're so weak!
(Thought Narration)
I'll explain...
The strawman Heroes gang
up on the weaker bad guy
underlings in order to defeat
them more quickly...
That was the most
pointless narration
I've ever heard!
Stay strong. The bad
guy boss must be nearby.
This is bad!!!
We completely forgot
to decide who would
play the bad guy boss!
What're we gonna
do now, Lee?
There is only
one option...
What... me?
Hey! Why is your
ally suddenly the
boss of your enemies?
Next time on
Strawman Heroes!
"Betrayal, Part 1."
See you next time!
You can't just
end the skit!
This entire thing is
getting completely out
of hand, here, Bushy Brow.
(Konohamaru)
We're losing our
audience fast!
What awful lessons
they're teaching!
It's a bad influence
on my smart little
sweet pea!
I'm definitely
going to the
school board now!
Please you guys... At the
very least, try to teach
the kids the difference
between good and evil...
Understood! The very
root of all evil...
The source of all
our problems...
It is all of you!
The rue bad guys
are the monster parents!
[gasps]
A mother who flies into
an uncontrollable rage
is way scarier than any
bad guy boss is.
Yep! You got that
one right, for sure!
You idiots.....!
Huh?
Team Super! Knock
all this nonsense
off!
And get lost!!!
[relieved chuckle]
[gasps]
[happy cheering}
[happy sigh]
[sigh] Boy that was
one crazy class...
I really doubt that
the kids learned
anything at all...
Iruka Sensei?
Huh!?
All of us learned
something very important
today in your class...
We see now that we
can't always let
our children do
whatever they want.
Sometimes they need
some stern discipline.
Frankly, we were all
in the wrong in this
situation.
Oh, thanks, ladies!
(Narrator)
Thus, thanks to Lee's
group, which was renamed
to "Setup and Punchline"
(Narrator)
The students of the ninja
academy started to like
a new word...
(Narrator)
In addition to "victory,"
they learned the value of
"Punchlines!"
This whole thing
feels so very wrong.
(Tenten)
On the next episode,
the titles are:
(Tenten)
"Hunting for Matsutake
Mushrooms!" and "Lee and
Neji Part Ways."
(Tenten)
PArt ways?
(Sai)
I could have
seen that one
coming...
(Tenten)
But, Lee & Neji might
argue sometimes...
(Tenten)
But, when push comes to
shove they respect each
other as rivals!
(Sai)
What did I say earlier?
Oh, next time, on Strawman
Heroes: Betrayal, Part 1.
(Tenten)
That was the preview!? But wait,
the Strawman Heroes aren't
coming back, are they!?