Welcome to the Hidden Leaf
Village. As you all know,
it's the home of the legendary
Naruto Uzumaki. But today, a
very unique ninja takes
center stage.
Idiot... Idiot...
Ahhhhh!
[gooney laughter]
Agh!
Go away!
[evil laughter]
Oh, we'll leave. As soon
as you give us the money!
Fork it over and
nobody gets hurt.
That's what you get
for borrowing it!
Leave me alone!
We'll be outta your
hair as soon as you
pay up!
Give it up and
this'll all be over.
You shoulda paid
us back sooner!
But, I can't!
We'll be up in your face
until we see the cash!
Then you won't have to
bear the embarrassment
anymore!
This is the perfect
crime, guys!
That is enough out of you!
Huh?!
Wha-?
Who said that?!
[excited gasp]
Ugh!
Lowlifes like you need
to be taught a lesson!
Huh?!
Who are you?!
As much as I would love to
tell you that I need no
introduction, it would be
rude of me not to provide
you a name. Even though you
three are wearing masks!
Get ready, because here
comes the intro!
No one can deter
me from my path!
My favorite words are...
Effort and guts!
I am a ninja who
lives for love!
The name of your foe...
Hah! Ya-gi-gi-gah!
...is Rock Lee!
Rock Lee is a ninja who
can't use Ninjutsu.
Idiot...Idiot...
[crowd chatter]
If you really think I am
going to let a trio of
thugs pick on a helpless
little girl, think again!
Scram, half-pint! This
ain't none of your concern!
You wouldn't be talking all
tough if you knew who we
were! I hope you like knuckle
sandwiches!
Don't say we didn't
warn ya, buddy!
Then you leave me no choice!
If talking will not fix this,
then punching will have to do!
Bring it on!
[attacking yell]
[barking]
[pushing grunts]
Ahhhhhh!
Doooooggg doooooo!
[attacking yell]
Ahhhhh!
[hysterical laughter]
Ooh! Nice undies, bro!
That's hot!
Polka dots are in!
You jerk! I'm gonna
get you for this!
That ninja is
pretty awesome!
Give it up! All he
did was fall down!
Huh...
That maybe how it looks
to the untrained eye...
...but, to those in the
know. That move lets one
win a fight without
hurting the other guy!
Elimination by
Depantsification!
No way! That
sounds so fake!
He just tripped over
dog poo, that's all!
He made them leave me alone,
and he didn't even have to
hurt 'em!
I can tell by the hearts
where your eyes should be,
that you are impressed by
my prowess!
Give me your hand.
Okay!
Give me a break!
Ahhh!
Tenten? Neji?
Look who left us
behind again!
We're supposed to be a
team, y'know! Which means
you can't just ditch us
whenever you feel like it.
Now, let's get going.
Sorry, but, could I get a
little more help before
you take him away?
Of course!
Idiot...Idiot...
Lone sharks, huh?
Yeah. They're picking on
me to get my dad to pay
back what he borrowed
from them.
Paying back a debt is
important, but picking on
those who are weaker than
you is not honorable!
Hm! That's a good
way to put it!
A friend of mine owed some
money to some people once,
and all they did was
bug him day and night!
Sir, the movie you rented,
After school Escapades, is
now overdue.
Sir, the movie you rented,
After school Ecstasy, is now
overdue.
Sir, you might as well
just buy the movie.
Ahhhh!
Overdue movies have
nothing to do with loan
sharks, you big dummy!
Do go on.
My dad's been working extra
hard to make enough money to
pay them back, but that's
not enough. If we don't
give them ten times as much
as he borrowed, they're
gonna mess up our house!
That's awful. Having
loan sharks threaten
your family like that.
The whole reason I came
to this village was to
hire a ninja to protect
my family from those thugs,
but then they caught
up with me on the way.
I'm just glad this nice
man was here to save me!
Save you? All he did
was pants a guy.
Please, Mister. You
wouldn't leave us high
and dry, would ya?
Do not worry! I am on it!
Uh, what are you
talking about, Lee?
Yes. We're already on
a mission, remember?
We will just have to
make room for this,
as well!
Do you mean it?!
Those thugs are toast! And
I am the toaster who will
bring them to justice!
Ahhhh!
You're not a toaster, you
dummy! That simile makes
no sense!
It's a metaphor.
Idiot...Idiot...
Hey, could you maybe
not walk like that
all the time?
What?! And ignore my
training?! No way!
We're here, you
guys. That's it!
Aha! Indoor plumbing dead
ahead! I really have to pee!
Uh! Be careful where
you're walking!
They set boobie-traps?!
Even worse! A stray dog
totally pooped out front!
Ah!
Noooooot agaaaaaain!
Ow!
I did not touch it.
That is all that
matters.
If our team ever has to
fight in a dog-park,
we're done for.
Are you okay,
mister ninja?
It looks as if those
villains have really
cleaned this place out.
Not just that. They've
turned off the electricity,
gas, and water, too. So all
I can offer you is cold tea.
Hold on. Do houses in
our world have utilities
like that?
Fear not, lacking hostess!
I will just have a coffee!
You dummy! She can't
make anything!
I shall pass on the tea,
also. Unless it's green
tea, then yes.
Why does no one
listen to me?!
Hold on! Rock Lee can
heat up the kettle for
us with ninjutsu! He can
shoot fireballs at it
or something, right?!
Fireballs are not
going to happen.
Huh. I'm sorry. Your powers
are way too important to
waste on tea.
Trust me, that
is not it.
I cannot use ninjutsu
ever! Get it?
Huuuuuhhhh?!
Whaddya mean you can't
use ninjutsu?! You said
you were a ninja! You are
a ninja, right?!
Totally. I just do
not have ninja powers.
Then, what was that
special attack you used
to save me earlier?!
Yeah, about that. I was
just dodging the dog doo
but it all worked out, so
I rolled with it.
More like rolled in
it, you goofy klutz.
A ninja that can't
use ninjutsu...
I will explain if
you give me a second.
When you said you'd make
room on the plate for my
problem, I thought you were
a ninja, not just some guy!
Stop yelling and I think
you will remember how
impressive Depantsification
was in action.
Just give it up!
You're nothing but a
liar, Rock Lee. If that's
your real name!
Please, you have to believe
me! I never meant to mislead
you! And besides...
Huh?
I cannot help that I am
the man you fell in love
with.
Oww!
We're not in a soap
opera! This is anime!
C'mon! I still bring a
lot to the table! Just
not, ninjutsu!
Get outta here,
you big faker!
[sigh]
She is really mad, huh?
Well, nothing you can
do if she's made up
her mind.
Guess we'll have
to move on.
Stupid liar!
Hm?
Him again?!
I told you to get
outta here!
Hiya, twerp!
Didja miss us?
The coast is clear! No
weirdo with a bowl-cut
this time.
It's time for the
finale, you guys.
You caused me a lotta
grief. It's okay, though.
Instead of paying me back,
I think I'll just take ya
with me! Bwhahaha!
[menacing laughter]
[scared whimper]
Oh no! This is it!
I think not!
Huh?
Him again?!
I was hoping you had
learned your lesson the
last time, but oh well! If
you do not want trouble...
Uh! Ugh! Ah!
...Leave that girl
alone already!
You got a lotta nerve,
trying to act like you're
a ninja!
Just hold on! Let
me explain myself!
Fake, huh? I thought there
was something fishy about
that pants attack!
If you can't even use
ninjutsu, we've got
nothing to worry about!
Ooh! This is gonna be fun!
Enough talk! Get 'em!
[evil laughter]
I do not need flashy
ninjutsu moves to win.
I have moves of my own!
Huh?!
Hah!
Leaf Crap Shoot!
Morning Coffee!
Ahhhh!
Raining Nosebleed!
Not bad, kid! But you're
gonna need more than
teakettles to beat me!
Bwahaha!
[fighting grunt]
[attacking grunts]
He's too good for
you! Run away!
No I can take this guy!
Oh, did I hurt you,
ninja without ninjutsu!
Mwheheh!
There's no way you can
beat this guy. Any ninja
who can't use ninjutsu
is just an ordinary person!
You're wrong.
Rock Lee doesn't need the
bells and whistles of a
ninjutsu to be special.
That's right.
Lee's worked really hard
on his hand-to-hand fighting
skills, but even that's not
what makes him unique.
He's one-of-a-kind
because of his willpower.
He never throws
in the towel.
Aghhhhh!
You idiot!
Hahhhh!
Hykahah!
Take this!
Did you just trip
yourself on purpose?
Hiyahhh!
[horrified scream]
Elimination by
Depantsification!
Ahhh! You little!
[panic gasps]
You win, little girl! No
amount of money is worth
this embarrassment! We're
never coming back here,
you guys!
Wait for us, boss!
[chuckling]
When it comes to using
ninjutsu, I stink.
However, I'm going to
be a great ninja someday,
with or without it!
I will never give up
until I reach that goal!
Now I know...
I was wrong!
I'm so sorry!
[dark barking]
[pushing grunt]
Ahh!
C'moooon, agaaaiiinn?!
Ahhhh!
[embarrassed gasp]
Idiot...Idiot...
Rock Lee wants to become
a great ninja, but he can't
even use the power that
defines them. Get comfy.
I think this is gonna
take a while.
To become a great ninja,
even without ninjutsu.
That's Rock Lee's goal in
life, and he works towards
it tirelessly.
When you said you had a
new training method, I
thought it was something
useful.
Of course it is useful!
What if you have to
slither up a tree?
Thanks, but no thanks.
And in case you'd
forgotten, I can use
ninjutsu.
I bet I could pull off
Naruto's transformation or
Shadow Clone Jutsu if I
really put my mind to it.
But! I want to do things
my way! I want to become a
great ninja without needing
ninjutsu, no matter how
long it takes me!
Lee! Neji!
We just got a new
mission, so get ready!
Rock Lee's Rival
is Naruto.
Wait. Baumkuchen?
Yep. Our client this
time around is a rich
old lady with a sweet
tooth.
She said the baumkuchen they
bake in the village is super-
popular, but they only make
fifty of them a day. Our
mission is to grab her one.
And how is this a
mission fit for a
ninja?
Hey! Every assignment is a
learning experience somehow.
We will give it our all!
Right, guys?!
Stop it! That is
totally weirding
me out!
Idiot...Idiot...
Whoa!
Look at this line!
We only make fifty baumkuchen
a day and fourty-nine of them
are spoken for! Somebody'd
better grab this voucher!
That's the final voucher!
Fly like the wind!
Mister! I really need-
Give it here!
Ahhhhh!
Bushy-brow!
It is Naruto!
This is Naruto Uzumaki,
in case you didn't know.
He's not always the sharpest
kunai in the pack, but he's
just as determined as
Lee to succeed! Above
all, he's a really strong
shinobi! And when he's not
guest-starring here in
chibi form, he's the lead
on his own show.
You are here for the
baumkuchen, too?
That's right, but not for
me. I'm just picking it
up as part of a mission.
Same as us, then.
I am sure Naruto needs
the last voucher and all.
I would step aside, but the
team's mission comes first!
Lee's a nice guy. I
would just let him
have it, but...
[fighting growls]
This is a mission!
No mercy!
So, the voucher?
Who wants it?
I do! Hand it over!
I am not trying to be
a jerk about it, but I
really need that
baumkuchen!
Not as much as I do!
I cannot back down
and neither can you!
Looks like we're gonna
have to settle this the
old-fashioned way!
[sighs]
Idiot...Idiot...
The rules are
simple enough!
Whoever grabs the
voucher first gets
to keep it!
That's it? Piece of cake!
Lee! You know he has
skills, right? This
won't be easy!
He's silly and forgetful
and clumsy and cheap and
perverted and greedy and
full of himself and an
all-around butthead and
dork, but he's a top-
notch ninja!
Why would you even
say all that junk?!
Now that's going
too far, Tenten!
I will give
it my all!
He is not someone you
can defeat without
proper training.
Not what I meant,
but whatever...
And his ninjutsu is at a
much higher level than an
ordinary ninja's would be!
That was just a
lame magic trick!
He has fought so many
villains. Here and a
long time ago, in a
galaxy far, far away!
Okay, that never happened.
Let's keep this in our
world, okay?!
Idiot...Idiot...
On you mark...
Get set...
Gooo!
[charging growl]
That baumkuchen
is mine!
Keep dreaming!
Ahhhh!
Bad luck there! I
guess it was not
meant to be!
[angry growl]
Sexy jutsu!
For reasons that are
pretty obvious, Sexy
Jutsu is one of Naruto's
most effective moves.
Ahhh!
I had a hunch Naruto's
ninjutsu would give him
an advantage!
Whatever! He lost the
lead because he was
being a perv!
That is not the case,
Tenten! It was because
I am the type of man who
lives by his instincts!
Spare me the lame excuses,
Lee! Stop twirling already
and get that voucher!
[painful grunt]
Ahhh!
Hey, Lee! Thanks
for the lead, sucker!
He is not the only one
who has got the Sexy
Jutsu up his sleeve.
Can he really imitate
any move, when he's only
seen it one time?
Hah!
You just changed
into a bikini!
This look will stop my
opponent dead in his
tracks!
You don't wear that
under your jumpsuit
all the time, do you?!
That's what
surprises you?!
[painful groan]
Not bad for your
first time out!
Would you two stop
drooling all over
each other?!
Nah. The nosebleed's from
hitting my head on this
branch when I jumped.
Honestly, I think you're
actually dumber than Lee!
I disagree!
It is time to make
my comeback!
Oh no you don't!
That cake is mine!
Here's another classic
Naruto move, the Shadow
Clone Jutsu. But you
knew that!
He's really beside himself.
What's the point of copies?
Having a bunch of himself
running around won't help
him win the race.
So that is how it is!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
That's incredible! Did
Lee really just-
Running fast to give the
illusion of multiple clones
is not Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Cut it out already!
That is it! I
will combine them!
Harem Jutsu!
Ahhhhh!
Ugh! The humanity!
Huh?! Neji fainting
doesn't give us any
cake! I'm tired being
the voice of reason!
Rasengan!
I won't let you win!
Too slow, two-piece!
[shocked gasp]
Nooooo!
That's all she wrote. I
got to the voucher first,
Bushy Brow! Better luck
next time!
I knew Naruto was good,
but even so, I guess I
have no choice but to
give up!
Huh?
No. I cannot quit.
If I quit now...
[baby crying]
Aww, please do
not cry.
Do I have to be
in this skit?
It is okay, Nejiko.
Be strong.
But this problem
is so hard, Mama.
That is no reason not
to try. Keep working,
you will figure it out.
Okay...
She is the best daughter a
mom could want, but she's
so quick to give up whenever
the going gets tough...
i wonder... where does
she get it from?
The other day, Sakura, this
girl who sits next to me
at school, was telling me
all about a cake she had
called a baumkuchen.
Oh? Is that so?
All the girls in class
were raving about it.
Ino's going to buy one
after school tomorrow!
Really...
Not that I want one or
anything. They cost too
much, and you already
work so hard for us, Mama.
Nenkinya baumkuchen.
Fifty made a day, 5,000
yen each.
Fancy store, charging
an arm and a leg.
We cannot afford it.
I am sorry, darling. I
had hoped we would never
have to spend this money.
She already goes without
so much.
I want her to have this.
Why are you making me a
baby in this dumb skit?!
This is no skit. It
is real life, Tenten.
How can you say that,
Lee?! You're not our mom,
I'm not a baby, and Neji's
not a girl!
Tenten, don't you get it?
I just wanted Naruto to
see how desperately we
needed the voucher. Go
for the heartstrings.
That was the plan!
No way is this silly soap
opera gonna change his
mind! I mean-
[sobbing]
He's crying his eyes out!
Bushy-Brow! I didn't see
how badly you needed that
baumkuchen before, but
thanks to your skit, now
I know!
Go on! Take the baumkuchen
voucher. No hard feelings.
That was all fake. You
do know that, don't you?
And, you know I used
ninjutsu, so I guess
that you won.
Naruto, I...
Well, see ya!
You know...
...that Naruto is a
real stand-up guy!
Well you got the
voucher, so at least
there's that.
Maybe I won the
baumkuchen, but as a
ninja and a gentleman...
...Naruto won,
hands down.
But the next time we
square off, I shall be
the victor!
Rock Lee wants to become a
great ninja, but he can't
even use the power that
defines them. Not only
that, but now he wants
to surpass Naruto, too!
Idiot...Idiot...
Ahhhh!
Sorry, we're out!
I called fifty a bunch
of times, but nobody
came up!
No baumkuchen!
We failed...
What do you mean "we"?!
[sigh]
Surpassing Naruto without
ninjutsu, huh? His path
will be an interesting one,
that much is certain.
Idiot...Idiot...
Today was a disaster!
What do you mean? I
thought it was our
best episode yet! Sure,
it has been our only
one so far, but still!
Best of one doesn't
count! What's wrong
with you?!
Not to interrupt but,
next episodes titles are,
"Love is a Part of the
Springtime of Youth," and
"Love Makes Both
Sides Crazy."
Love, huh? I take that
stuff very seriously!
Just you wait!
Sakura, my darling!
This is gonna be
a mess.
See you next time!