Have you ever wanted
something so badly you
were willing to wait in a
long line for it?
A ride at an amusement
park?
A very special purchase?
Or a delicious bowl of
ramen?
Finally, morning
training's over.
Now, we can look into
getting some lunch.
Any preference on that,
Lee?
Let me see...
Yesterday we had pork curry.
The day before that was
ground beef curry.
And three days ago
was green curry!
That makes the choice
clear: We top things
off by getting the
ultimate curry!
[groaning]
It will be amazing!
What is it with all the
curry this month?! This
crazy curry festival of
yours needs to end!
Well, strictly from a
business point of view,
if we keep pushing curry,
a food company might
notice and decide to
sponsor the show--
Leave stuff like that up
to the producers!
How about ramen, then? We
haven't had that in a
while.
[growling]
Ramen, you say? I'm
sold! Let's head over
to Ichiraku!
For those of you who
don't know, Ichiraku is
a famous restaurant in
the Hidden Leaf village,
and Naruto's first
choice for ramen!
Save Ichiraku Ramen!
What?! Ichiraku might go
out of business?!
Yeah, unfortunately.
A famous ramen chain from
the Flavor Village called
"Tasty Ramen" just
opened up a store
directly across the
street, and it's taking
away all of Ichiraku's
customers.
Look there's another
ramen spot over there.
But look at the line for
the one behind us. It's
gotta be a much better
place!
People see that line,
make assumptions, and hop
right in.
It's almost as if just
the act of lining up for
that place itself is
becoming a new trend.
Anyway, because of them,
no one's going to
Ichiraku anymore. The old
man and Ayame are really
depressed about it. And
I'm getting really
worried about them!
People are suckers for
two things: famous names
and long lines.
And unfortunately, it's
survival of the fittest
in the business world.
Always has been.
But what is happening
here is not fair! It is
one thing if their food
is better, but they are
winning due to a catchy
name and fad status!
Naruto, listen!
Huh?
You can count on the
three of us to help save
Ichiraku!
You mean it? Alright,
Bushy-Brow! Let's do
it!
I sincerely appreciate
the offer,
But making ramen is too
hard for a bunch of
novices to waltz in and
do it right away.
[sighing]
Your skill lies
in eating ramen, not
cooking it!
Hey!
You need not worry. We
have no intention of
changing the flavor.
[nodding]
Your ramen has been
beloved by the villagers
here for many years. A
true local favorite.
Um, from that montage, it
looks like Naruto's been
the only one eating
anything here...
Listen: if you simply
alter your business
strategy a bit, I
guarantee you can bring
in customers and beat
Tasty Ramen!
Come on, pops! What do
you say?
All right. I can't turn
away enthusiasm such as
this! Let's give it our
best shot!
[giggling]
The first thing we must
do is learn as much as we
can about our enemy.
Which means it is time
for some recon.
I see, so we find
out about their
recipes.
Don't you dare!
First of all, the enemy
is sure to recognize us.
And secondly, I don't
think my stubborn old dad
is going to line up at a
competitor's store and
eat his food.
Hm.
No way! He's already
there?!
Dad, please! Show a
little pride, will you?
Jeez!
Talk to him, Naru--
[gasping]
What the-?! Not you,
too?!
Huh?
Do not worry yourself,
Tenten.
We do not need
Naruto or Mr. Teuchi
to spy on the flavors
of the enemy!
Neji!
That's right!
They don't know Neji's
face! He should easily be
able to get a seat and--
Byakugan!
[gasping and groaning]
That's what you meant
by "spy on the flavor"?!
Even if you can see the
dish from here, that
still doesn't mean...
... you can tell
what it tastes like!
It's thick.
A very thick
pork-based broth, with
two types of mackerel,
bonito and vegetable
dashi.
In spite of its
heaviness, it has a
smooth, mild flavor.
You really can see the
flavor?! That's some
Byakugan.
Okay then. Now that we
have our information, we
need to formulate a
Double Fish Pork
Ramen Counterattack!
"Double Fish" what?
Since when are you so
knowledgeable about
ramen?
First off...!
...We need to come up
with the right side
dishes!
Indeed, we do.
Dumplings, gyoza, fried
chicken...
There are a lot of good
side dishes that go with
ramen!
Wow. You know what?
It's true that we work
very hard on our ramen
dishes, but we tend to
neglect the sides. I'd
never thought of that
before.
And so!
I came up with a
"barbecue lunch set"
side dish!
Are you crazy?! A lunch
set is way beyond a side
dish! That's a whole meal
in itself!
It's a ton of food!
And as an additional
measure to counter the
thick broth of our
enemy...
[screaming]
What'd you do
to him?!
We shall lay the service
on even thicker! Get it?
Your head is the only
thick thing around here!
One thing's got absolutely
nothing to do with the other!
Whoa! For some reason,
I'm burning with youth!
Especially in the
head area!
That's because that
stupid wig is making
you hot!
Don't forget: Our enemy
isn't just laying it on
thick!
They manage to keep it
all in check with a
smooth, mild flavor!
I remember. So then...!
Here!
No!
A Go-Go Girl?!
This approach with the
wardrobe allows us to
balance our thicker service
with something smoother!
This isn't food service,
it's fan service!
And this isn't smooth,
her outfit shows no
restraint at all!
None shown here. Not
here, either!
There's nothing left to
the imagination!
[sighing]
Then I suppose I need to
keep things more in check?
Huh?!
Here!
Is that a school
swimsuit?!
Showing less skin
doesn't fix the
fundamental problem!
This changes nothing!
It doesn't matter what
kind of service we're
offering,
it won't make any
difference if we don't
have any customers!
That is true.
Here's an idea: why
don't we use ringers?
Think about it: just
seeing the line seems to
draw people to the other
ramen house.
That's true. There's some
psychology to making people
want to stand in line.
Ringers might be
the ticket.
I like this plan! We
should give it a try!
Here is our ringer:
Sakura!
We need more than just
her!
What's going on here?
Er, I'm sorry, Sakura.
Look. No one's gonna get
in our line just because
she's in it!
Not true! We did!
She only works on you
two!
Hey, look! A line!
Let's get in it!
Get back in the kitchen,
dammit!
If you're here, who's
gonna make the food?
Just leave the cooking to
me!
No! You leave it to the
professionals!
That hurts.
Now that we are set, we
simply wait for the
customers to roll in.
Yeah!
[sighing]
But even after all that,
no customers came back to
Ichiraku.
Aw, man. Why did it not
work?
Despite our planning, I
think our business plan
got off on the wrong
track.
"Got off on the wrong
track"? I'd say it
went straight off the
rails and flew off into
space! It was a disaster!
I'm sorry about all this,
kids...
You tried so very hard to
help me out.
Ugh. Pops...
I've got a lot of
confidence in my cooking
and my dishes. I'm just
disappointed I'm not
getting a chance to
compete on flavor.
All those customers are
lining up because of the
name of the place, or
the line itself.
I wish we could show them
how good our food is
without having to try it.
"Without having to try
it", you say...
We totally can! There is
a way to do just that!
Oh, yeah? How exactly
do we pull that off,
Bushy-Brow?
Just leave everything to
me!
Hello! We are here today,
on location, to find the
best ramen in the Leaf
Village!
And joining us on this
culinary quest is one of
the most well respected
gourmands in the village,
Choji Akimichi!
Thank you. Glad to be
here.
I'm gonna stuff myself
silly!
What's going on here?
What's the plan?
The only way to convince
people of a restaurant's
quality is a positive
review from a famous food
critic. And if such a
critic were to sing its
praises in front of that
line...
Hey, that ramen place
over there looks pretty
good!
I think I'll
give it a shot!
Me, too!
Bam!
We will have an even
bigger line than the one
over there.
I get it, but why Choji?
That is the ingenious
part of the plan! Choji
even looks like he could
be a famous chef!
Food always look yummier
when a fat person is
enjoying it!
I am not fat!
[gasping]
I'm just big-boned!
Okay, everyone! Time to
dig in!
Right! Bon appetite!
Goodness! This is
delicious!
What do you think, Mr.
Nejiyama?
What? Me?! I--?!
Why'd you put
him on the spot?
Well, it's, um I'd
say it's--
It's Eight Trigrams and
Sixty-Four Palms of
deliciousness!
That made no sense at
all!
It was the best I could
do, okay? Man, being a
food critic is so
complex...
You're over thinking
this. Get over yourself,
already!
What are they doing over
there?
I don't know and I
don't get it.
This is bad, Lee. They're
getting turned off by all
the confusion!
This is great! Another
round, please!
Nice going, Choji!
If he eats a few more
bowls, we can easily
convince people the ramen
here is that good!
Man, this barbecue lunch
set is outta this world!
No! No! You gotta
eat the ramen!
How could my brilliant
side dish backfire like
that?
Lee, you are the biggest
idiot on the entire
planet! How could you be
so stupid?!
We worked so hard and you
ruined it! You ruined it!
Don't worry!
I've got this!
Neji! Please, turn this
around for us!
The flavor is
Byakugan-tastic!
That is the
opposite of helping.
Wait! All I'm trying to
say is that the flavor is
bright and clear!
No, there's nothing but a
black void awaiting us
now.
Choji! Hold on, please!
Try some ramen instead!
Hang on, I haven't
finished what I
already--
Eat it and tell us what
you think!
Back off! Let me finish
my beef first!
[gasping]
No! The ramen!
[screaming]
Sakura! Watch out!
Should've known!
Time for Leaf Hurricane!
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
Hey, wait a minute! This
stuff is really tasty!
I like what I've tasted
so far! I'm gonna check
that place out!
Oh, yeah!
Huh?
[clamoring]
Gimme ramen!
I want some ramen!
Dad, it worked!
Hey, Naruto! Lee!
Thanks so much!
[laughing]
Thus, Ichiraku escaped
bankruptcy.
But the sudden upswing in
customers was not without
its consequences. It left
Lee and the others with
empty bowls and empty
stomachs.
I want my ramen!
As our story opens, Lee
and his team are just
coming back from a
mission.
Thank goodness. We're
finally home.
"Thank goodness" is
right! That mission was
brutal. I need to get
home and take a break.
You are in need of a
break, you say? Okay!
All right, I will squeeze
100 apples and make us
the most refreshing juice
you have ever tasted in
your life!
That's no break at all.
You're just painting
yourself right back
into a corner.
I continue to train my
body, even when I am
resting.
Suddenly, I am burning
with passion!
You don't have to burn up
to make juice! Can't you
regulate your temperature
any better than that?
[sighing]
Vacations are for
Training!
Bushy-Brow refuses to
rest?
Yes, exactly.
Ever since fall began,
it's been one event after
another.
And he makes a big
production out of
all of them!
On top of that, Guy
Sensei always makes him
do these bizarre,
weird exercises with
him on our days off!
Yeah, that's bizarre and
weird all right. What are
they doing?
I'm worried about what
this is doing to his
health.
As am I. There is such a
thing as over training,
you know.
If he hurts himself,
it'll all be for naught.
Hmm...
Well, I completely
understand what you're
saying. But if this is
what Bushy-Brow wants,
why not leave him be?
See ya!
[sighing]
Later, that evening...
Thanks for the meal!
So, Lee! Exhausted from
another day of training?
Now's the time to fill up
on your favorite food,
and take a nice long
rest.
[groaning]
I cannot eat another
bite.
You didn't eat a thing.
Although I've never heard
anyone say that in their
sleep before.
He really does need to
get a proper break, and
soon.
Hmm.
[snoring]
Hmmm...
Agreed. That is cause for
concern.
You think so, too, Lady
Tsunade?
Even if you're fit,
overtraining will have
the opposite effect.
[struggling]
Additionally, as a
teenager, Lee's body is
still growing.
Wait, why are just his
eyebrows still growing?
That seems kinda weird.
In order to grow in a
healthy way, the body
needs plenty of rest.
What's going on here?
This is definitely not
balanced, it's nothing
but hair!
Look how I've grown!
It's not even him
anymore!
We agree, of course. But
even when we tell him to
rest, he ignores us and
keeps going.
We need a way to force
him to take sit back and
take it easy.
Huh?
Of course!
The answer is Labor Day!
Labor Day? How so?
Labor Day was originally
created for laborers and
tradesmen to celebrate
their contributions, and
offer mutual gratitude to
one another for all their
efforts.
Somehow watching this
doesn't make me feel
grateful at all.
In fact, I don't even
want to watch this!
It's too much for
me to handle!
This year, I'll add
another facet to the
holiday...
... I'll order everyone
in the village to rest
and take it easy.
If it's a rule, Lee will
have no choice but to
comply!
Lady Tsunade...
Thank you! Thanks so
much!
[giggling]
And so, Labor Day came.
This year, the Hokage has
declared that everyone in
the village has to take
the day off and rest.
So make sure you actually
take it easy today. Okay,
Lee?
Understood. shall take
the day off, as ordered.
I think it's
working!
He's finally learning the
importance of rest and
relaxation.
Well, since I have the
entire day off now, I am
free to train to my
heart's content!
That dummy hasn't learned
anything!
Lee, these are Lady
Tsunade's orders! You've
gotta obey them!
Look at it this way: try
to think of resting as
today's mission. Got it?!
Yeah, I got it... Orders
are orders.
[yelling]
We demand the right to
train!
The Hokage is taking away
our human rights to train
as we wish! She must go!
Enough already!
[grunting]
You just don't
get it, do you?
It looks like he needs a
lecture directly from
Lady Tsunade herself.
Why did you follow me
here? Don't you get it?
I told you all to take
the day off!
Her head is totally in
vacation mode.
Yes, but I do not
understand what the
problem is, Lady Tsunade.
For starters, this hand
doesn't feel right.
She's completely focused
on the game.
"This hand"? You are
saying I just need to
rest my hands?
You mean fold? You don't
know anything, do you?
Wait, maybe she'll
explain things to him
after all.
This is no time to lie
down and quit! The real
fight starts now!
She's even more
oblivious than Lee!
Now I am even more
confused than before.
What will happen if I
don't rest?
"Get too full of yourself
and treat your underlings
to lunch! You lose your
bonus!"
You shouldn't even have
to ask... You grow weak.
Speaking of which, it
seems Lady Tsunade's mind
is growing weak...
She won't be able to
convince Lee in her
current state...
Did you say "weak"?
You feel I am growing
weak? No!
I didn't expect that!
Maybe now Lee will...
When you are this beat
up, you must put all
things aside and rest.
Yes! It's working!
I will not allow my body
to grow weak.
I have to train harder
than ever before! Time to
work!
That's the complete
opposite effect!
And now he's run off...
Would you please help us
stop him, Naruto?
I told you, I think you
should just let him do as
he pleases!
If you help us, we'll buy
you all the ramen you
want!
Yeah! Sure thing! Count
me in!
Where'd you come from?!
No fair, Choji! They
asked me first! I'm in,
too! That ramen is mine,
you hear me?!
No way! You snooze,
you lose!
Those fifty bowls
of ramen and ten barbecue
meals have my name all
over them!
You're adding things! I
never said that!
[giggling]
I'll use my jutsu to
transform into Sakura.
Then, I'll invite
Bushy-Brow out to lunch.
After that...
I am so elated you want
to have lunch with me,
Sakura! Of course I
will join you!
I will stop
training right away!
It's foolproof!
I'm a genius!
Nice! Simple, but
practically guaranteed to
work! Great idea, Naruto!
Give Lee, Give Lee, leap
into the fray, forget
common sense, throw it
all away!
Hey, Sakura!
Bushy-Brow! What do you
say we grab some ramen
together, you know?
Hi, Naruto.
What? How'd you know?
Naruto, you dimwit...
Alright. Now it's my
turn.
I'll lure him in with
some BBQ-ed goodness.
Hey, Lee! Wanna grab some
lunch with me? I've got
some coupons.
We can eat 'til
we're completely
stuffed!
Wow! Thank you so much! I
was just starting to get
hungry!
[eating]
[slurping]
Whew, I'm full!
Couldn't eat another
bite!
Thank you for inviting
me, Choji! Now I am all
fueled up for my
afternoon training!
No problem! Good luck
with all that!
You just wanted to
eat a big lunch,
didn't you?
Now he's more
motivated than before.
Oh, sorry about that.
I've had it!
I give up!
You'd think all of
Bushy-Brow's skits
would have you exhausted.
Why are you still at
it on your day off?!
Wait a sec, the skits? Of
course!
What do you mean, Tenten?
Those stupid skits Lee's
always making us do!
Think about it!
We can use a skit to
teach him the importance
of proper rest!
One of those skits,
huh? I'm not too thrilled
about it, but it may be
our only shot!
Naruto, Choji, will you
two help us out?
Well, if you insist.
If at first you don't
succeed, fry, fry again.
Try, not fry.
Say it ain't
so, Doctor!
Hm?
You're saying my dad
is going to--
Yes... He's got about a
week at the most.
Oh, no...
Daddy, make sure you rest
up, okay?
Hey, sis, when is Lee
coming home? He should be
here.
It shouldn't be long.
I've got an old friend
out looking for him right
now.
Tenko, are you--are you
going to call him?
Well, I was planning on
it, yes...
[coughing]
That boy abandoned our
family to run off and
chase his foolish
dreams...
Don't you dare call
him, you got that?! I
won't speak to him even
if he does show up.
[coughing]
We lost Mom when she was
very young.
That left Daddy the
responsibility of raising
all three of us by
himself.
Thanks to Daddy's
efforts,
my big brother
Lee was able to pursue
his lifelong dream of
becoming an actor...
... but daddy never
forgave him for leaving
us.
Even though he talks
tough, I'm sure that
Daddy secretly longs to
see his boy Lee again.
Lee. I beg you. Come
back...
Please! It's been ten
long years...
[crying]
Oh, sis...
Great job, Tenten!
There's no way
Bushy-Brow won't
be moved!
[crying]
Fine! I will stop
training!
He'll be bawling
like a baby!
And he'll finally give
his body the rest that
it needs.
This will actually
help us get through
to him!
Huh?
What are all
of you doing?
We finally get the day
off, and you are
performing skits?
Huh?!
Anyway, I must go work
out now. Bye!
What?!
Don't stop the Lee!
Today, Tenten and the
gang learned a hard lesson:
That no skit can convince
Lee to stop training.
But make sure you all get
plenty of rest, kids!
Lee, you butthead!
Next time is "Caring for
Animals is Hard Work,"
and "Howl at the Naruto."
Okay then, I will put my
heart into it and howl
out!
[howling]
Lee, I don't think it's
supposed to be literal.
[howling]
Whoa, what's that? I
think the Nine-Tails is
reacting inside me!
[howling]
Stop howling at each
other, you morons! And
the Nine-Tails isn't a
dog, so cut it out!
[howling]