[growling]
When it comes down to
the nitty gritty, battles
between women are climactic
clashes of pride...
"The Warring Chef Triad"
(Narrator)
But let's turn the clock
back a few hours first...
Boy! Camping is such
a blast! Is it not?
Nothing like
spending a summer
roughing it, huh!?
Hey, don't get complacent.
This is survival training,
not a vacation!
I do not get it.
You think we are
being complacent?
What makes you
say that?
Your entire existence!
Now save the damned
sunscreen for the beach!
Man, this is the worst.
Camping is such a drag.
Especially the
cooking part.
It'll be hard.
Seriously...
How can we make
enough for everyone?
If we don't catch
any fish, nobody's
eating tonight!
(Choji)
Woah, got one!
Finally!
The girls are in the
mountains gathering fruit..
...if we don't catch
enough fish for everyone,
they'll rip us a new one.
Do girls rip
them? I thought
it was just us!
[toot]
Everyone rips 'em!
[toots]
ARGH!
Put a cork in it,
you nincompoops!
He said rip us a new
one, not rip one!
Being the foil here
all by myself makes
me appreciate the
girls more than ever!
Appreciate the girls..?
Oh hey!
I know, why don't we
just ask the ladies if
they want to handle
the culinary work?
Ugh, no one's doing
anything until we've
caught enough fish
to feed us all.
I don't know if that's
such a hot idea, Lee--
we can't make them do
everything...
Are you kidding!? Just
cuz we're girls doesn't
mean we're gonna do all
the work!
-What she said!
Man, I can hear em
already-- I'm not
messin' with that!
Me either.
They're 3 of the proudest
girls I've ever met, It'd
be a pretty tough sell...
You're right, they
are proud...
That gives me
an idea!
What? They're
still gone?
Maybe they didn't
catch any fish?
(Naruto)
Give me a break!
Look, I'm telling
you, you're wrong!
Hey, what's
going on?
We're deciding who's
going to cook the
fish we caught.
There's just one
problem...
Everyone is pulling
for their own team, so
things are starting to
get a little heated...
Nobody cooks like
Sakura! She's the
best there is!
[echo]
She's the
best there is!
Please! Tenten
is a hundred
times better!
[echo]
Tenten is a hundred
time better!
Hello!? What about me!?
Oh, come on,
guys! Stop it!
This is silly!
I appreciate the
compliment, but
there's no need
to fight!
I bet Tenten can't
make anything except
Chinese food!
What...
Sakura's too clumsy!
The best she could
possibly do it roast it!
What!?
Seriously, you guys,
knock it off already.
It's not like fighting
will help anything...
Oh! I beg to differ!
Tenten's cooking skills go
way beyond Chinese food!
Making ramen in a
cup has nothing to
do with cooking, Lee!
You guys are crazy!
Sakura can do more
with a fish than
just roast it whole!
We can't eat it
like that, Naruto!
Ah, come on you guys,
does it even matter?
It's like arguing
about eye boogers
and nose boogers-
...compared
to Ino....
Hey! Is that
all I get!?
I am not letting
that one slide!
You can say
that again!
Lee...
Naruto...
Just who's cooking is
the eye boogers and
whose is the nose boogers!?
Technically speaking,
the eye boogers would
taste better!
-You're not objecting?
Heck, as long as it's
still edible, I don't
care if it's a little
gross...
[grunts]
[birds chirping]
Idiot... idiot...
[scream in pain]
Choji! Are you okay!?
Let's just back
this up.
What're you
saying, exactly?
Maybe we're mistaken,
but it sounds like none
of you think we can
cook for squat.
Oh, trust us! We don't
think you can't cook,
we're 100% certain of it!
[growls]
[birds chirping]
Idiot... idiot...
[scream in pain]
Sai!!!
All right-y then!
We'll show you
nay-sayers just
how well we can cook!
And we'll find out
who the best is in
the process!
[laughter]
Fine here's how
we'll do it...
Put something together
from all the food you
gather in the mountains
today.
Then, whoever's dish
gets the most votes
will be the winner. OK?
-Mhm!
-Fine by me!
(Narrator)
And thus, the three
girls went to war.
[cry of fear]
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
I never imagined
your plan would
work so perfectly.
They're a proud bunch,
those three. Take advantage
of that and they're like
puppets on a string...
Yeah but we are sort
of tricking them,
though, aren't we?
I am starting to
feel a little
guilty, you guys.
I hear ya...
Just focus on the fact
that we'll be eating
Sakura's home cooking
soon!
[giggle]
Hooray for Sakura's
Cooking!
Hooray! Hooray!
Hooray!
And for Shikamaru's plan!
Hooray! Hooray!
Hooray!
Hooray for Sakura's
Apron!
Hooray! Hooray!
Hooray!
Ah man, those two are
so positive, they
could live through
the end of the world.
Yeah.
The competition this
afternoon shall consist
of one sixty minute
round! Begin!
It is an all
ladies cooking
showdown!
How do you see
it playing out,
color commentator
Nejiyama?
Oh will you
shut up!?
(Neji)
Their skills are
more or less equal--
--so the competition
will ultimately come
down to who found
the best ingredients.
Well put! Just like
they always say--
--there is no amount of
makeup that can transform
an ugly ingredient
into a princess.
That made no sense!
It is hard to
be a woman...
We're reporting
live from the kitchen!
Sakura appears to
be making some type
of fish curry at
her station.
(Lee)
MY taste buds can
hardly wait!
In related news, here
in the kitchen, our own
station apparently has a
meaty curry in the works.
(Neji)
Another curry dish!?
This competition is
really heating up!
Reporting from the
kitchen, the fruit
is incredibly ripe
and very sweet!
Who said you could
taste test any of
the food!?
It seems like all
3 chefs are taking
the curry route today!
The ingredients will
have a huge impact
on the outcome!
Woah! Reporting
from the kitchen!
Sakura's taking it to
the next level and
adding lobster!
I thought the rules
dictated all ingredients
were to come from the
mountain...
It was swimming up
a local waterfall!
This just in--
Ino's using some
very pricey black
Wagyu beef.
It just so happened
to be out rock climbing!
Oh please! There's
still a big fat
price tag on it!
Reporting from the
kitchen! I'm taking
it to the next level
too!
Could you for once
control your appetite!?
In a bold move, it
looks like chef
Tenten isn't adding
any new ingredients.
Unless she's got something
to counter lobster and
premium beef, I'm afraid she
just doesn't stand a chance!
Chef Tenten has just
tossed in a terrible
trio of habanero peppers!
Got em at a
store at the
foot of the
mountain...
Don't be so honest!
Couldn't you at
least come up with
an excuse!?
Lee has always
liked spicy food!
Um, I like it
up to a point...
(Naruto)
Gyah! Sakura!
What the heck
are you doing!?
Gyah! I hate
spicy food!
That's not what I
had in mind, Sakura.
Darn it! I'm
gonna lose!
No way! You're
winning by a mile
after what they
all did...
I'll just have to triple
my secret seasonings to
three tablespoons of chakra!
What does that
even taste like!?
Oh yeah?! Well how
about I add FOUR
tablespoons of chakra!?
Big deal! I'll
add a whole bowl
of it!!
This is total madness!
[birds chirping]
Idiot! Idiot!
(Ino)
I'll make chakra soup!
(Sakura)
Whatever! I'll make
chakra stew!
(Tenten)
I'm making a chakra
combo platter, beat
that!!
-Okay! Bon Appétit!
I wonder what it
will taste like...
Seriously, it
looks so gross!
-huh?
Don't be shy! Go
ahead and dig in!
-Yes ma'ams!
[gulp]
[gag]
BLEGH!!!!!!
It is delicious!
It's out of
this world!
Man, I don't
believe it...
Glad to see that
everyone's happy!
[chomping]
-Hm!?
BLEGHHHH!!!!!!
-Wow.
(Sakura)
You idiots!
Huh?
All that food you
just ate was packed
with chakra!
You goons, you thought
you had us dancing in
the palm of your hand,
didn't you!?
"Hooray" for just
what, exactly?
Hooray for Sakura's
cooking! Hooray,
hooray, hooray!
(Tenten)
You're going to eat
every last bite of
curry, are we clear?
[crying]
(Narrator)
One this is clear in
today's competition:
The men lost, big time.
(Narrator)
Early to bed, and
early to rise, and
all that...
(Narrator)
What about you? Are
you an early bird?
(Narrator)
Today Rock Lee is...
...off to radio
calisthenics!
It's too early to be
so energetic, Lee.
You're too high
strung... chill.
[birds chirping]
Idiot! Idiot!
Of course I am!
Radio calisthenics are
a hallmark of summer,
like going to the mountains
and the ocean!
Is it really that
big a deal--? Training
is training, isn't it?
This goes above
and beyond!
The exercises are being
run by none other than
Guy Sensei!
Oh good, won't
that be novel...
Lee, I've come up
with a new method of
radio calisthenics.
Hope you're
ready to disco!
Yes, sir!
You are really
excited, aren't
you, Sensei?
Let's show everyone
what hot blooded
youth is all about!
(Lee)
You are too hot to
handle, Guy Sensei!
(Guy)
Wanna swim across
to shore!?
(Lee)
I will not loose!
[splashing]
This is not
gonna end well.
Tenten, how can
you say that?
We are his pupils!
It is our duty to
support our sensei!
(Radio)
Raise your arms
over your head!
Oh, listen! They've
already started.
Let's get going!
Already started..?
(Radio)
And one, two, three,
four, one, two...
(Radio)
One, two, three,
four, one, two...
"Time to Tone Down
Guy Sensei"
It's hot enough this
summer and you want
me to exercise with
Guy Sensei..?
Ugh, just thinking
about it makes me sweat.
I'm sorry... He's
a little intense!
I'm not much of an
early riser, ya
know what I mean?
Yeah, you'd burn off
an entire day's worth
of calories if you ran
into Guy in the morning.
What a drag.
I'm gonna pass.
I'm sorry. Old man,
what do I do??
Go with beef
over rice, or
rice over beef!?
Well, they've got
all their reasons.
It looks like
radio calisthenics
is a bust this year.
It's too bad. Seemed
like a lot of their
reservations had to do with
Guy Sensei's personality.
Well, I suppose if nobody
is showing up, Guy Sensei
probably isn't sticking
around than, either.
(Radio)
Raise your arms
over your head.
Guy Sensei?
What? You wanna know why
I'm still doing that
calisthenics class? That it?
Yes. It just seems a
bit pointless to, you
know, keep going after
nobody showed up.
Yeah, it's true!
It seems nobody wanted
to come out and exercise
with me, I guess...
It doesn't help that
it's the middle of
August...
This is the month when
everyone either goes back to
their hometowns, or packs their
bags for a dream vacation.
Stop, please! I'm
not seeing this, I'm
not seeing this!!
It's gonna give me
nightmares for weeks!
By now they've probably
all forgotten I'm even
out here in the morning.
Just been me, myself, and I.
Please, anybody,
scrub the images
I just saw from
my brain!
And yet, when all
is said and done,
somebody might still
chance upon this spot!
What if somebody
showed up tomorrow
and I was nowhere
to be seen..?
As long as there's a chance
that even one person will
show up, my radio and I will
be right here waiting for them.
So that's why
you go it alone...
I understand!
You just leave
everything to
us, Sensei!
We will find a way
to get some students
out here for you!
You'll see!
I swear! We will
save your disaster
of a class for you!
Wow... Lee...
Thank you...
Sometimes I forget
what wonderful
students I have!
Gu... Guy Sensei!
[little sob]
Lee!!!
Guy Sensei!
For God's sakes! It's
hot enough out here,
will you knock it off
with the crazy!?
What do you say we start
by taking a look at all
the different responses
we got..?
Good thinking! That'll
help us formulate a
decent game plan.
Now, where do
we begin?
I know just who
to start with...
It't hot enough
this summer and you
want me to exercise
with Guy Sensei??
Ugh, just thinking
about it makes me sweat.
She has a point...
The three of us are used to it,
but to a normal person, Guy
Sensei's manly hot-bloodedness
can be a tad overwhelming.
[spinning shout]
Guh-oof!
Uh, are you okay
Guy Sensei??
Uh, yeah..! Got hit
with a little verbal
wind-style jutsu,
that's all...
Oh boy, this is
awkward-- You
already look
totally heartbroken!
So anyway, we need to
find a reliable way of
coolingGuy Sensei down!
I suggest... We
can use a gi-normous
fan!
Then his temperature
will drop like a rock!
Not his physical
temperature! What
is wrong with you!?
Moving on to the
next response...
I'm sorry... He's
a little intense.
Let's face it. I know
the three of us are
used to it... but, to
the average person...
Guy Sensei's intensity
is utterly ridiculous.
[gurgles]
[cough]
Guy Sensei! Are
you okay? What's
wrong!?
Yeah, sure. got
nailed with a
verbal water-style
jutsu is all...
Don't throw in the
towel already, geeze!
So we just need to
lighten him up a
little big, is that
it? I have got it!
We just gussy him
up in a sheer, yet
casual new outfit!
Nobody said anything
about his clothing, Lee!
Oh, right. Then
how about this!?
Somehow that makes
him seem even more
intense!
And last but not
least, there's
this one...
Yeah, you'd burn off an
entire day's worth of
calories if you ran into Guy
first thing in the morning.
Again, I know the 3 of
us are used to it, but
to a normal person...
Sometimes Guy Sensei can
be a lot to deal with in
the morning!
Oooh..?
Ooof.
Guy Sensei!
Okay, so essentially,
Kakashi Sensei was saying
that one should avoid Guy
Sensei in the morning, right?
I have it!
He can teach the
class at night!
I dunno. He just
looks like a tired
crazy old guy now.
This should keep
things nice and
cool now, right guys?
Oh yeah, totally.
So cool, I'm starting
to get the chills...
...From the creepiness.
Huh?
I'm really sorry,
everyone...
Looks like I
actually needed
my students to
save me for once.
We haven't saved
you at all!
If anything, you're
worse off than when
we started, are you
kidding!?
Chin up, team!
All that matters
is we did our best!
We didn't accomplish
anything! What are
you so proud of?
Relax! It is fine!
We just need to
wait for everyone
to show up!
(Narrator)
BUt, just as Tenten feared,
no one showed up to do
calisthenics with Guy Sensei.
[bird chirping]
Idiot!
It's hot enough during
the night summer, and
you expect me to go
exercise with Guy Sensei?
Ugh, just thinking
about it makes me
toss and turn!
I-I'm sorry... He's
a little bit intense,
isn't he?
I'm not much of an
early riser, know
what I mean?
You'd just end up
doubling all the stress and
exhaustion of the day if you
ran into Guy at night.
What a drag...
I'm gonna pass.
I'm sorry! Gimme a
sec. I'm trying
to think, here...
Should I stuff the
beef in rice balls,
or wrap them up with
it instead?
[sigh] I cannot
figure it out!
What are we
doing wrong!?
Maybe we over-
learned the lessons
of history--
I think we've been
hoisted by our own
petard.
Oh, we're hoisted, all
right. We're hoisted,
hosed, and hopeless.
I say we call
it a day...
Well the three of us
should keep showing up
at least. He is our
Sensei, after all.
(Guy)
Wait! You've got
it all wrong!
Don't think I do.
We got a report of
a suspicious man in
the area.
I'm just doing
radio calisthenics!
Yeah, you can tell
us down at the
station, weirdo.
(Guy)
Excessive force! You
no good thugs! I
know your type!
Alright, you've
done your time.
No more funny
business, okay?
Yes, sir...
No one seems to be
waiting for ya...
Don't you have anyone?
I, uh...
I have somewhere
I've gotta be, sir...
I have to go...
Huh? Go where?
Radio calisthenics.
Hey you guys...
Sorry Guy Sensei...
I... I...
(Guy)
I should be
apologizing to
you...
[gasp]
You've all been waiting
for me, and I wasn't
able to be here to run
the calisthenics class.
Guy Sensei?
It wasn't just
them....
Huh?
The three of them have
been running around all
over this village...
...rounding up as
many people as they
could find to meet
you when you got out.
This is... I have
such wonderful
pupils I don't know
what to say...
Well, you seem pretty toned
down, so I guess we can get
through this without burning
too many calories...
Alright! Shall
we then?
Show us the new and
improved calisthenics
you created, Guy Sensei!
Okay then! Here
we go!
Now, raise your hands
high in the air, and
let's shake and wave our
way to a good sweat!
(Guy)
Annddd up!
(Radio)
Now grab a torch and
keep to the rhythm!
Dance, dance, dance!
Anndddd up!
Ha! Hoo!
Ha! Hoooo!
Huuuuuuuu ha!
Uh, what?
(Narrator)
They had waited for
Guy to get out of jail,
(Narrator)
...but skipped out before he
finished his special brand of
...exercise...
(Narrator)
Hang in there, Guy!
Keep fighting, Guy!
(birds chirping)
Idiot! Idiot!
(Lee)
Tune in next week for "Road to
Guy!" & "The Amazing True Story
of the Leaf Film Festival!"
(Lee)
So, Tenten, any
thoughts on this?
(Tenten)
Huh?
"I Rock Lee was grateful for the
chance to play a hero who
protects Sakura from evildoers-
(Tenten)
-but even more so to be able
to play her lover as
well..." What is this!?
(Lee)
I am preparing an
acceptance speech
just in case.
(Tenten)
You don't need an acceptance
speech, that's not what we're
doing next time!