(Narrator)
Behold! The famous
Great Stone Faces.
The face of each
Hokage has been
carved into the
cliff side...
Here is the fifth
Hokage herself,
Tsunade!
Let's go, Shizune!
Yes, milady...
Huh..!?
Hey, fellas! Any of
you feel like parting
with your money today?
"Even Hokage Go Bald"
We're training with
ninja tools today!
What kind of tools?
Check it out!
[gasp]
You... handed me...
a pair of nunchaku..!
Rolling up these
scrolls takes forever.
Hey, Tenten--
Look!
Huh? Are nunchaku
not your thing?
The truth is... I
love them so much!
He's amazing!
Look at him go!
Watch out!
ARGH! You just made
Lady Tsunade bald!
She's gonna have our
heads when she sees that!
I am so sorry!
[running]
Come on, Lee! Hurry
up! We have to get
it back to normal!
After we fix her hair,
maybe we can get my face
back to normal, too?
(Thinking)
When it comes to Lady
Tsunade, Tenten would
do anything...
[gasp]
So that's Tsunade,
the fifth Hokage, huh?
We'll sniff her out
and then we'll
snuff her out!
Who are those ninja!?
We have to warn
Lady Tsunade!
(Gambler)
I roll first!
Here we go!
(Gambler)
Three and four: seven!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven.
"Run the 3-legged race
with your klutzy kid at
a family picnic--"
"--Waste your chakra,
lose the race and
your next turn!?"
That's not fair!
[laughing]
Watch and learn.
Hiyaaaa!
Double sixes!
Ten, eleven, twelve.
"Arranged marriage
to an oil tycoon"
"Get oil fields in the
number you just rolled
as a wedding gift!"
Outta sight! Twelve
fields all for me!
For reals!?
When it comes to gambling,
they usually call her
"The Legendary Sucker," but
she's cleaning up today!
I've got a bad
feeling... Hm?
Mount Fugi, a hawk,
and an eggplant?
What the heck
are you doing!?
Guy!?
There are rogue
ninja targeting me?
When they told me
about it, we sent
Team Guy over
right away...
But we didn't have
time to coordinate
our disguises.
I'm glad you were so
quick about it and all,
but those are the worst
disguises ever.
Mhm.
But Mt. Fugi!...?
We heard that you were
playing down here at
Tansakugai, so we wore
outfits to bring you luck!
Why!? Why am I
the eggplant!?
Lady Tsunade..?
I... I got this
for you.
A good-luck charm?
Wow! Thank you!
[happy sigh]
You are taking this
seriously, huh, Tenten!
Course I am!
Because... I'm a big
fan of Lady Tsunade--
She's always so
strong. It's just...
Oink?
Wow! It really
worked, master!
Very well done,
Sakura!
(Thinking)
Since I can't use medical
ninjutsu, I couldn't
become her student.
I don't really feel
like I've earned her
respect, that's all...
This is my
chance to show her
what I can do!
Lee! I'm so proud!
I know just
how you feel!
You do?
I will give this
mission my all
as well!
Please, let us escort
you back to the village,
milady. You'll be out of
harm's way there!
Not so fast!
You think you can clean
us out, then leave before
we can win any back!?
Fine by me!
[gasp]
[laugh] Let's see
how you do at cards!
Doesn't matter what we
play. Lady Luck's on my
side today, no matter what!
Hm, we'll see
about that!
Come on! I drew the
old maid again!?
Guy Sensei, are you
sure it is okay for
us to be playing?
If guarding Lady
Tsunade calls for
it, it's all right.
The rules for Old Maid
are pretty simple, Lee.
Just make sure
you're not the last
one to have her.
Byakugan!
There she is!
On the far right!
They don't mean
a person, Neji!
Technically speaking,
Lady Tsunade is more
of a spinster.
She is over half a
century old, though
you would never know
it just by looking!
Shut up, Lee!
Sure, maybe she's hiding
under a ton of makeup,
but 53 is basically the
new 47!
I'm still young enough
to break you in half!
That... that isn't
what I meant, Lady
Tsunade! I'm not
trying to say..!
Hey! Do you know who
else puts on a good show?
Huh?
Hey 'ooooo!
She is not
a wrestler!
[grunt, groan]
Is that one Tsunade?
She isn't
bald on top.
Our target's supposed
to be a master of
ninjutsu, so, let's
use that to find her.
What do you mean?
[snicker] Just leave
it to me, I've got
something in mind!
Sorry to barge in, but
my friend is very sick!
Is there a doctor in
the house?!
Why are you coming
in from the closet?
This is anime, Lee.
Don't sweat the details.
As a matter
of fact--
Why, yes! I
am a doctor!
I don't think
that's her...
Fine. If that's the
way they wanna play
it, I'm game!
Pardon me, but, is anyone
bald here? I could just
look but I've got an eyepatch.
Ooo! Bald!
Right here!
How are you bald?
I owe you both an apology.
We were in such a rush, I
could not get a real hawk
outfit...
Bald eagle was
all they had!
[groan]
Long story short,
your quest for
baldness has come
to an end!
I don't think
this is gonna
work!
Hey! We are not scrapping
this mission just yet!
I wasn't gonna bust
this one out, but it
looks like we've got
no choice!
Pardon me! It's weird
to ask, but I need to
know if someone's curves
are over 100 centimeters!
That would be me!
One-hundred-twenty
centimeters!
That is not
what he meant!
Outsmarted by
an eggplant!
I am not giving up!
Me again!
Is anyone here wearing a ton
of make-up in a desperate
attempt to pass off as something
they're clearly not?!
Me! I really caked
it on for the
snowlilne!
Are you for real!?
What is your deal!?
Stop being so vague!
Let em know exactly
who we want!
Okay, fine,
just calm down!
This one ring
any bells!?
Is there anyone here
who resorts to violence
at the drop of a hat...
...has horrible luck with
gambling, has even worse
luck with the fellas...
...is fighting a losing battle
against gravity and wrinkles
which is a big problem because
she's still single at 53!?
Grrrrr!
Gravity and
wrinkles?!
(Gambler)
Hold on, blondie!
If you're trying to
win and run, you and
me got a problem!
Watch out!
Got them all!
Good thing!
They looked
sharp...
L-Lady Tsunade!
Could you be
any more dumb!?
No way! All the kunai
we deflected still
found a way to land
right on her head!
Don't worry, milady!
I'll save you!
How bout you take the
kunai out first...?
[angry mob]
You are safe now!
I don't think we'll
be seeing them again!
[grunt]
Lady Tsunade!
All of the men we
kicked away somehow
landed on her head!
What are the
odds of that!?
You guys had better not
be doing this on purpose!
Meddling do-gooder
ninjas!
How dare you throw
kunai at Lady Tsunade!?
Your luck's run out!
Argh!
She's bald!!!
On the bright side, at
least she now looks like the
carving of her on Mt. Hokage
So I guess it
all worked out!
-Yeah! You're right!
It did not all
work out!!!
Ahh!
[chuckle]
So she was the
one all along!
Now's our chance!
Yeah!
[coughing]
Lady Tsunade!
Take this!
Woah! What
the--!?
Her good luck charm
attacked us!
(Tenten)
You like my weapon
summoning?
I put a special stamp
on the charm I gave her
that can shoot out
weapons, when needed.
[gasps]
No matter what,
I will keep Lady
Tsunade safe!
Ultra Divine Blade Storm!
[screaming]
We quiiiiiiit!
Lady... Tsunade.
I'm sorry!
All I wanted to do
was protect you, but
those two ninja almost
carried you off!
Tenten...
(Thinking)
Whatever she says,
we deserve it.
[gasp]
You really came through
for me, did you know that?
[gasp]
They would've made
off with me if you
hadn't stopped them
when you did...
I'm proud of
you, Tenten.
She... she just
said she's proud
of me!
Neji, Guy, and
Lee as well.
You guys played an
active roll in
today's events.
-No need to thank
us, Lady Tsunade!
I've got something
special in mind for
you three!
-This is gonna hurt!
[crying in pain]
(Narrator)
Thankfully, their hair
will grow back someday.
Probably...
Maybe you should
wear a hat...
(Narrator)
A Tanzakugai casino...
Within, a gambler who
doesn't know when to
fold em...
Right hand onto red,
25. Tongue to yellow, 7.
(Narrator)
Wait, they're
playing that ?!
[grunt] I'm out!
[slurp] Heh heh!
You thought you could
out-stretch the likes
of me?
I'm chakra-ing out.
All right! That's three
million chakra and 2
chocolates!
You really cleaned
up, Lord Orochimaru.
Must've been the
snakeskin wallet I
bought off the late-
night shopping channel.
They said it would
bring good luck.
What are you going to
do with all that chakra
you just won, anyhow?
What do you think.
Kabuto? I'm going
to use it!
"Orochimaru is Persistent"
More ninja tool
training coming up!
Hey! Where's Lee?
He's up there, repairing
the damage he did to
Lady Tsunade's likeness.
Uh, you think he's
gonna be okay on
his own?
That's a pompadour!
Why does he think
that's even an
option!?
Hey, Lee! How come
you gave the Hokage
a pompadour!?
Oh! Sorry, Tenten!
I am trying my
best but I am
not good at this!
Too scary!
What're those curls!?
Bald again!
[sobbing] Fingers!
Why do you not
listen to my brain!
[crying]
How are you so
bad at that!?
I think I've got
a fix for this!
If we plant trees for
her hair, changing her
'do will be a lot
easier, right..?
Beats carving!
Oh! I never would
have thought of
trees!
Why'd you make
her a samurai?!
She is right. This
will only work if we
plant a lot more of them.
Not gonna lie,
I kinda dig it.
You just gave
her an afro!?
Not a problem!
Just a bit off
the top, eh?!
Now she doesn't
even look like
a girl!
Leave her hair
alone already!
What's that?
What do you mean?
[chirping]
The forest is alive!
[sighs]
Huh!? This is not the
time for cute baby birds!
(Lady Tsunade)
Exactly!
Lady Tsunade!
If you're gonna do
such a bad job of
it... step aside!
Who's that?
[rumbling]
[gasps]
(Lee)
Up there! That
is...!
There is a joke
here. Think,
Lee, think!
[groans]
This is no time for
a joke, Rock Lee, just
be good children and
cower in fear!
Here's the deal- I
summoned Manda with
the chakra I won in
the Tanzakugai--
-- And now I'm
going to use him to
wipe out the Hidden
Leaf Village!
[hiss]
He is a very
persistent man!
I'll handle him!
Not without me!
-Summoning Jutsu!
[gasps in awe]
The village is in danger.
It looks as though there
is definitely going to be
a fight now!
I don't go out of my way
to get into scrapes with
anyone, but if it's for the
sake of my friends, I'll do it!
Gamabunta and I can
handle this so please
just stand back---
[slurp]
Katsuyu, no!
Uh, maybe he shouldn't
have come out here on
an empty stomach?
Now we're right back
where we started!
I guess it is
up to me!
Wait, you can do
summoning without
using ninjutsu?
But of course,
Tenten!
Summoning Jutsu!
Aw, why me!?
Sticking Neji in a
turtle outfit doesn't
count! Not against a
snake the size of that!
It is true the snake
is larger than us, we
could not find a
bigger costume!
Hello! Could you
zoom in until Tenten
is out of frame?
If he can shoot us
at just the right
angle...
Forced perspective!?
It is easy on the
budget, and a
practical effect!
That doesn't
work in anime!
[screaming in fear]
[shouting]
Lady Tsunade!
Argh!
So... who should be
next on the Hidden
Leaf ninja buffet?
(Thinking)
It's working! Last
week's failures are
just a bad dream!
(Thinking)
Lord Orochimaru is
completely different
today!
But how does all this
play with the target
demographic!?
What if they want
funnier?! It's so
hard to read the
viewers these days!
We gotta get out
of here before it
digests us, Lady
Tsunade!
That light!
My goodness, don't
tell me you were
swallowed up as well!
Uh, Guy?
What are you
doing here?
Ah, yes. You see
I was training up
on the mountain...
Today I will sing
without blowing out
the flame of this
candle.
What does that
help with?
Both the candle and I
were slurped up by
this giant snake!
But I didn't blow it
out, so, there's that.
I still don't get
what that's
training for!
What do we
do now!?
Do not worry! I
am prepared for
this moment!
I will throw this
super-spicy curry
into Manda's mouth.
After that...
Fly true, curry!
Uhh...
Is it working?
Byakugan!
[grunt] It's so
good... but it's
so hot!
Guy's eating
the curry himself!
Ahhh!
This is no time
to be stuffing
your face, Guy!
Calm yourself, Naruto.
I developed a device in
case a day like this should
ever come along, and now is
the time to give it a try!
What kind of device?!
Dude, are you breaking
the fourth wall!?
What's wrong!?
Afraid of the big
bad snake, are we?
I dunno, I think we've
put the series leads in
too much peril...
Our chibi design is
better for comedy.
Well, live and learn.
We cannot keep
fighting it like
this!
Huh!? We were
running away! That
wasn't fighting!
Hey, isn't there an
extra face up there?
One, two, three,
four, five... six!
(Neji)
Number six is
Guy Sensei!
Goodness, you do not
think that this is the
hero he built to champion
our darkest hour!?
(Lee)
The giant robot...
Might Guygatron!
Might Guygatron?
Fight for great
justice, Might
Guygatron!
That's right!
Take him down!
Pitiful. It's just
a giant doll.
We'll use chakra
threads to make
it fight!
Focus, focus, focus!
Neji, you take
the right half...
Tenten, you take
the left half...
Now work together!
And you!?
Eyebrow duty!
That doesn't
help at all!
Is that piano
wire?
And now! The
final form!
Huh?
Super Attack!
Robo-Sexy Jutsu!
It's showtime!
Tell me why this
giant robot is
wearing a bikini!?
Oh my!
What kind of idiot
do you ninja take
me for!?
Ow, ow ow!
Ooof! Oof! Ooof!
Grrrr!
You think yourself
a match for me?
[cocky laugh]
Argh! Since the Robo-
Sexy Jutsu did not stop
him, there is only one
option left to us!
But, Lee..! That
move is so hazardous!
Will it even work
with a robot?
Just one way
to find out!
Right!
W-what? How are you
still on your feet?
Now! And a one...!
And a two..!
And a three!!!
Now you die!
Shimura Style, Wow!
Curses! Foiled
again!
It's better this
way, really.
(Narrator)
And so, the Hidden
Leaf Village was saved.
Might is right!
Get it!?
[laughter]
[groans]
(Tenten)
Really? Come on...
(Narrator)
Everyone came out safe
and sound. And they all
lived happily ever after.
Does this look
"happily" to you!?
(Tenten)
Hey! Who's that voice
who always tells us
about the next episode?
(Lee)
Wait, you do not
know either, Tenten?
(Narrator)
Who me? Why, I'm just the
narrator of this fine show. Now
go on with the preview...
(Tenten)
What's your name?
(Narrator)
It doesn't matter...
Just--
(Lee)
How tall are you?
Any hobbies? What is
your blood type?
(Narrator)
Just say the titles for
the ne
xt episodes, you
moron!
(Lee)
Okay! Next week is "Hinata is
Neji's Cousin," and "Hinata's
Weakness is Naruto."
(Narrator)
See, that wasn't
so hard.
(Tenten)
He's scary!