Another peaceful day in
The Hidden Leaf Village.
[scream]
On the other hand,
maybe not.
Guy Sensei,
what is wrong?!
[gasp]
[pained tumble]
What is going on?
It better be a matter
of life and death!
Huh?
[breathing]
Guy Sensei, what
happened to you?!
Might Guy: A Story of Love
and Hair!
This was supposed to be my
normal shampoo, but look
what it did to my hair!
This stuff here?
Byakugan!
This is Orochimaru's doing!
No surprise!
Do not be so concerned!
What are a few strands
of hair?!
Lee is right about this.
Cheer up, Guy Sensei!
You mean you...
...don't really care?
Of course not! Do not forget,
my friend, you are the Leaf's
Noble Blue Beast!
No one's
going to care!
[laughing]
[crying]
[throwing grunt]
[pained yell]
Guy Sensei!
[groan]
Good morning, everybody.
Did you come for training?
No, sensei! The truth of the
matter is, we came here to
bring you a present!
And here it is!
Huh?
You guys are great.
Something feels off.
Something more,
in his face?
It might be too much.
Let's try this.
Wait, I know!
Hey! That
actually works!
Nothing creepy
about it!
Guy Sensei has
been re-born!
[chuckles]
Thank you, guys.
For the thought.
But the truth is,
it's pointless.
Without any blood pumping
through it, I won't feel
any youthfulness wearing it.
[sigh]
It's just a wig.
Is it really that
big a deal?
Can't really have
a wig with blood
pumping through it.
In that case...
We will find a
wig that is alive!
Huh?
For example,
this one will
grow!
But his head
isn't a vase!
Alright, then, this
matches the shape
of his head, perfectly!
He's not a
giant mushroom!
[sigh]
It's no good. I appreciate your
efforts, but I don't feel a
partnership or any affection
to any of those choices.
So that's it.
For now,
I'm done.
I'll see
you later.
(Rock Lee)
There must be
some solution.
Blood pumping...
Affection!
What have you
come up with now?
Guy Sensei needs
a pet wig!
What does that
even mean?
It would be a living creature
that you treat with love!
Just as you would a pet!
Andif it is a pet,
Guy Sensei is sure
to fall in love with it!
That sort of
makes sense!
Time to get
ourselves in
gear!
Huh?
In gear
for what?
Come on, Ino!
Please!
Lee!
Do a Mind Transfer
into this wig!
Huh?
What in the world
are you thinking?!
If she controls the wig
with her Jutsu, it will
become a real pet!
That's ridiculous!
Not if it ends up
helping Guy Sensei!
Just forget
about it!
[humming, gasp]
Help us please!
Please!
[scream]
Please, Ino?
Come on, Ino!
Please help
us! Please!
Okay, fine!
Good morning, Guy Sensei!
I have come to introduce
you to what I hope will
be the ultimate partner!
Oh, it's you, Lee.
I'm sorry, but I
really don't want to-
This is for you!
Would you mind
taking a look?
What is this?
Behold, the ultimate tailed
beast! His name is Cuticle!
He has a hundred-thousand
tails! Can you believe that?
Thousands upon thousands more
tails than Gaara's One-Tail or
Naruto's Nine-Tails! Every one
of those little hairs is a tail!
I see.
Thank you.
Frankly, I'm not sure
what's going on here.
But I'm thankful for the
burning concern you have
for your poor old sensei.
Sir!
Cuticle.
Arise and
come forth!
This is the hundred-thousand
tailed beast? I don't quite
know what to make of it.
This is not a good start.
I need to open a line of
communication, to make
him feel the love.
Greetings to you my most
exalted master! I am Cuticle!
You can talk?!
Oh yes, master! And I give you
my word that I intend to work
very hard, to make you love
and accept me!
That's gonna be
some trick, if he
pulls it off.
I believe you.
Very well, starting
right this moment...
...you will be
my partner!
(Wig)
The wig is youth!
The wig will make
everything alright
again!
The wig will make
everything alright
again!
This might work,
after all!
Are you ready,
Cuticle?!
(Wig)
Yes, my master!
Death Strike!
Time to experience
Cuticle Frenzy!
Reload!
Yes sir!
Time for another
Death Strike, and
Cuticle Frenzy!
I don't understand
how that move works.
I am ready,
my master!
All right..
Go!
Beginning the
Youthful Shampoo
Dance!
Splendid! What a hot-blooded
soul you have! You're the
greatest partner, ever!
What does his
soul have to do
with anything?
Frankly, I
can't imagine.
I've been dying
to see this!
This film is better!
I would prefer to
watch this one, instead!
Huh?
We're watching
this one!
No, we are
watching mine!
This one!
No, mine!
He's arguing
with his hair!
We should throw
them a comb. It
might shut them up.
[yell]
[pained grunt]
[running]
Hmpf!
Huh?
Cuticle!
Here, master!
We'll watch whatever
movie you want!
I'm so sorry, master!
My bald spot isn't the same
without you sitting on it!
I miss your scalp!
This is like watching a bad
TV movie. Does he know he's
doing this cheesy scene with
a wig.
As the days passed, Guy's
relationship with his hair
grew deeper and deeper.
This whole storyline
is giving me heartburn.
[gasp]
I can't take much
more of this..
Bathing with Guy Sensei,
sleeping with Guy Sensei,
no more! No more!
[screams]
I can't do this!
I'll die!
[moans]
Sorry, Ino.
Sorry isn't going
to cut it!
I won't recover!
[crying]
Looks like she's
pretty much done.
Hm? Hey, look...
His missing hair
is starting to
grow back!
Yes! Time for
the final stage!
You're leaving me?
But why?!
Thank you for everything you've
done. I appreciate it. But I
must return to the Tailed Beast
Village now.
Please, Cuticle!
You have to understand.
This was always going
to be temporary.
Don't go! I thought we were
going to be together forever!
[crying]
Listen to my words carefully,
Master, and trust what I say.
Your true partner...
...is up there!
You have to
believe me.
[gasp]
Citicle!
My master. I beg you.
Live happily with your
real hair!
Thank you, Cuticle.
I promise, I'll never
forget you!
Seriously, guys.
No more.
Noooo!
Lord Orochimaru!
What's wrong?!
I accidentally used the shampoo!
The special stuff I made for
that man!
How can I crush the Leaf
Village, looking like this?!
It's going to be alright,
m'lord! I, Kabuto, predicted
this accident might happen,
and prepared a contingency!
Come forth the
hundred-thousand
tailed beast!
Gee, I kinda
like it!
He should. That's as
good as he's looked
in years!
Today, we join our three heroes
as they are practicing their
moves and polishing their
[coughing] teamwork.
They have been training-
[coughing]
Hello! Are you all
right up there?
Sorry, folks.
[coughing]
My throat's been bugging
me for the last few days.
That is very
unfortunate.
[sigh]
I haven't had a day off
since I can remember. It's
starting to catch up with me.
Would you like to
take a little break?
Say whaa?
Substitute Narrator!
You sure you can
handle all this
narrating, Lee?
In my opinion,
I thinkI should
do this.
Nothing to worry about!
I will do my usual superb job,
and everything will work out
great!
That's what worries
me more than anything.
Here we go. Welcome to the
Hidden Leaf Village, where we
find three particular shinobi,
training their tails off.
There are only
two of us here.
Regardless, our hearts remain as
one even if I am not present.
Now, the introductions.
Right now, Lee?
This is Tenten. A very kind
young woman, but a scary one,
who can summon a variety of
weapons in an instant.
Her punchlines are sharp. Lady
Tsunade is her heroine, but she
has many inches to go to catch
up to her, bust-wise.
She is strong-willed, but
doesn't always make the
right choices.
This is particularly true when
it comes to meals. Yesterday,
she ate a lot of ramen and
gained a ton of weight-
Enough, already!
Now Neji...
[gasp]
Huh?
He loves to
cross-dress.
That's all you
have to say?
I'm not doing it
for fun, you know!
What you see are two everyday
friends, who go to a normal
school and have become normal
ninja.
But what makes them and their
entire team unique, is their
third member.
How to describe him? He is
a cool, strong man everybody
loves.
He is known as the
genius of hard work,
and his name is Rock Lee!
You expect people
to buy that?!
I am really getting
the hang of this!
You're definitely losing
touch with reality.
I'm gonna go. I'm leaving
everything in your hands,
alright?
No problem at all!
Have a relaxing vacation,
Mr. Narrator!
Yeah. I'll try.
Training for combat is the
light that fills our world.
hope that fills my heart.
It is the training that
ultimately unites us.
We yearn for the clear
light of training.
What in the world are
you babbling about?!
The first task for
these dedicated
ninja are push-ups.
Tenten dropped
down and took on
the challenge.
Bending her arms,
she pushed her
muscles to the limit.
Neji was next.
He dropped down and
began his workout.
He put his feet together,
kept his back straight,
and pushed off the ground.
Their goal was to do ten
thousand repetitions.
Huh?
That's crazy!
For their next challenge,
both participants must climb
a waterfall, starting right
in the middle.
Let us hope they are able
to get through unscathed.
[gurgly]
[scream]
Neji!
At this point,
let us go to
Tenten.
Forget it!
Moving right along...
Next on the schedule
is shuriken practice.
Thank heavens..
Finally, something
normal.
However...
However?
I really have a craving for
pudding. Let us do some
pudding-cooking training,
instead.
Are you serious?
[gasp]
A young girl with a broken
heart, meditating as she
is blanketed with snow.
A lone seagull cries out.
Neji's Byakugan prevents
his eyes from drying out.
Byakugan!
The pair now switch to
harsh spiritual training.
This is nuts, Lee!
Our heroes now find themselves
preparing to do the latest
make-out dance!
What sultry secrets will
they be forced to reveal?
Huh?
Whoa! That is almost more than
either of them can resist!
Only the highest-caliber
of ninja can withstand
such temptation!
The bell is about to ring,
and their trial will begin!
[groans]
I have to rely on my
Byakugan to get me
through this successfully!
Just a little bit more
and I'll have it.
Neji!
[groans]
What is the point
of all this?
Kakashi Sensei's the only one
who reads this make-out stuff,
anyway!
Did I hear
my name?
[gasp]
Hello..
And thanks.
[moans]
Hey, guys!
What are you
up to?
Shhh!
We slipped away when he wasn't
looking, and we don't want him
to find us!
There you are, Naruto Uzumaki.
Always running around.
Just another Leaf Ninja.
Lady Tsunade ought to
whack you one.
That is, as long as it does
not make you transform.
Uh, what's going
on here?
Unfortunately,
you're about
to find out.
Oh, there you
are, Naruto.
I was just about-
Sakura Haruno!
Huh?
If the village is a
goddess, here is its
angel. Its radiant
beacon of hope!
Huh?
Her forehead
shines brighter
than the stars!
Wider than the ocean,
standing tall and proud like
Mt. Fuji herself, blazing
forth like the morning sun.
I am but a gaseous nebula of
love, being sucked into the
black holes that are her eyes!
Why is Lee
narrating?
It's a
ong story.
Let's find someone
else for him to focus
on, so we can escape.
If we can start him
on Guy Sensei, he'll
forget all about us.
So far, we have apparently
overlooked one of our most
important players!
Oh, yes.
You forgot
about him!
To make up for lost time,
you need to tell everyone
about him!
I understand.
'Him', you say?
Meanwhile...
Uh, excuse me, but you're
very early. I haven't even
studied my lines yet.
Only one thing comes to mind
when you see this Prince of
Antagonism, Orochimaru...
Just one thing?
You know
what it is!
[panic groans]
Swallow 'em whole!
Yes.. and then?
And then..
You have to..
spit 'em out!
Apparently, his trademark eye
lines are just makeup. Looks
like his real eyes are very
small.
[paniced yell]
[sigh]
It's really weird.
I've been dying to have a
vacation for so long but...
...I wonder what's
going on back
at the village.
Maybe, maybe
they're fine
without me.
[sigh]
Mr. Narrator!
Huh?
We need to
talk to you!
What?
You mean me?
Wha--? What are
you all doing here?
You have to come
back to the village,
right away!
Huh?
Seriously!
Right now!
I just introduced him.
Lee, have you
forgotten about
him?
Him?
Come on,
you know!
Oh, you
mean him!
[chuckles]
I almost forgot
about you,
Kakashi Hatake!
Hm?
What brings you all here.
It seems like the show's
doing fine.
Fine, my foot!
What is
going on?
You're just in time, Lee!
There's someone else in the cast
who wants you to introduce him!
There is a man who can smash
fate with his fists, a man who
can stand against the heavens!
That man is..
um, Guy Sensei?
I can't even
read in peace.
All done!
No, you're not!
Someone over
there is begging
to be intro'd!
This man is a traitor to the
village, Sasuke Uchiha. He does
not really fit in, which is why
he does not appear on the show.
Stop that!
[grunt]
This is the problem with Lee
narrating! He's gonna keep
bringing up things we're not
supposed to mention!
Please come back
to work, Mr. Narrator!
Hm!
Uhh...
All right.
Ahh!
Okay, let's
do this!
Well, that does it. It covers
everyone who is anyone around
here. Now it is time for our
heroes to train.
I don't think
so, Lee!
Huh..
Uhh.
It's time to
take him down,
Mr. Narrator.
By popular request, a lone
narrator returns from a beach
resort, where he leaves behind
the sound of crashing waves.
Huh?
After much pressure, his final
battle is about to come to an
end.
His very dangerous opponent:
None other than Rock Lee!
What?!
Rock Lee, adored disciple
of Guy Sensei, known as The
Leaf's Handsome Blue Beast!
But his true nature is simply
that of a training-aholic.
Desperately in love with Sakura,
his lack of game stymies his
efforts.
But that's not
all, folks...
The truth is, he owes Tenten
three thousand, one hundred
eighty ryou.
And he makes Neji cross-dress
because he really thinks it
looks cute!
[sigh]
[applauds]
As it happens, that vacation
was exactly what I needed.
[clears throat]
It returned my voice
to proper shape!
I am so glad
that you're back!
Please, my friend,
make sure you take better
care of yourself from now on!
You're the only
narrator any of
us need, or want!
Mhm!
Aw, thank you guys!
I was starting to worry that
the show really didn't need
me, in order to continue!
But I was wrong.
To think all of you
appreciate me so much.
I plan to return the favor,
and help improve the ratings.
I'll be there to narrate all
your embarrassing secrets!
[paniced screams]
One thing stays the same!
The narrator knows all!
Next time, be sure to catch
'Save Ichiraku Ramen', and
'Vacations Are For Training'!
I have never gone a single
day without training!
Didn't you tell me you spent
your entire last day off,
sitting at home and binge
watching a bunch of movies?
I was still in training,
though! Those movies were
treasure troves of useful
genjutsu techniques!
Like I said, they're not
genjutsu, they're skits!
All those references are
turning you from a ninja
into a comedian!