(Narrator)
Akamaru seems a bit
down as of late.
(Narrator)
Poor little guy...
Akamaru!
[sad grumble]
You see?
I wonder what's
wrong with him...
Maybe it's puberty.
He might have had
a growth spurt, but
it's not puberty.
[tweeting]
[sad grumble]
Aww... Oh!
Maybe it's--!
"Dogs Need Dog Friends"
(Sakura)
Friends, huh?
There aren't really
any other dogs for
him to be friends with,
huh? What can we do?
Hmmmmm...
It's not like they
have to be ninja
hounds or anything.
Oh! I know!
A dog café!
-Dog café?
Yeah! Take a look! It's
a café where you can
bring your dog to play!
Hey! It says they
have good waffles
there, too!
Oh! And the latte
art's so pretty!
And check out this
hot waiter! A nice
treat for the pet
owners, too!
This place sounds
amazing! Let's go
there!
Mhm!
Well... but...
maybe...
I mean, to be honest, we
could take it or leave it.
But for little Akamaru's
sake, we have to go!
It's the right
thing to do!
Yeah! Akamaru needs
friends, doesn't he?
Yeah... I suppose...
Oh, but there are
four of us, and he's
the only dog. That'll
seem kinda weird...
Hmmmmmmm...
Hold on! I know!
Huh?
Excuse me, Neji?
Uh, Yes, Lady Hinata?
Uh, well I- I was
wondering if you'd
be my pet.
HUH!?
Well, that's one
way to ask him.
[horrified grunts]
Sure, No problem.
Whoa! Really?
Hey, Naruto..
Would you like to
be my little puppy?
Heck yeah I would!
Come on, seriously!?
And you? How
about it?
Sure! I've secretly
always wanted to try
dog food! It's so
meaty looking...
With no hesitation.
Oh! Then...?
Very well, I--
I understand! It is
like disguise training.
You can rely on me!
I thought so...
Everyone's on
board, who knew?
Sorry we're late!
So, what's up?
Woof!
(Kiba)
Dog café?
[dogs barking]
Oh! Look at all these
cute little dogs!
Alright! Let's find
you some friends,
Akamaru!
Yeah! Let's do
it! Are ya ready?
woof!
Check out the
hottie over there!
Oh, what the heck?
Might as well try to
get a date as long
as I'm here, right?
(Sakura)
Hey, look! That guy
over there's not
too bad, either!
[giggle] Wow!
So, he's a--
[gasps]
What's wrong?
What is it?
Uhh...
Oh! Excuse me, Garon?
Could you get him a
chicken roll with some
veggies on the side?
And for myself, I'll have
a fresh herbal tea with
honey. Make sure the water's
nice and hot, okay?
What the--!? He's
being so casual!
Hold on, that guy's in
the Akatsuki, right?
It's Kisame and
Samehada.
So, uh, that
thing's a dog then?
Somehow I don't
think so...
What do we do!?
Making friends
isn't an option
with him around!
Aw! That hot guy's
leaving, too!
He's driving everyone
away!
This is awful! How are
we supposed to find
Akamaru a friend now?
Well he doesn't
actually have a dog
so maybe we can
ask him to leave?
But that wouldn't
be fair, we don't
have real dogs either.
I just can't.
And I can't
either!
Wow! Who knew dog
cafés were so intense!
Oh my! What an adorable
bunch of dogs you have!
What are the names of
these cute little guys?
No way! He
approached
us first!
Um, well um,
that one there's
Akamaru.
And... let's see, the
other ones are...
Leemaru, Nejimaru,
Narumaru, and Chomaru!
And what about...
your ... uh, puppy?
This is Samehada.
And he's acting
normal...!?
Is that so? Samehada's
certainly a rare name,
isn't it?
What breed is
he, anyway?
Good job, Ino! Perfect
attack strategy!
Oh, he's a bit
of a mutt.
He countered!!
So, that really
is a dog, then?
No. I've run into him
a time or two before.
There's no way that
thing's a dog!
Come on! Of course
it's not a dog!
Does he feed it
dog food though?
What courage Akamaru
has! Get him. boy!
[whimper]
[roar]
[scared whimper]
Poor little guy!
Do not worry! Your
brave display will
not be in vain!
I will go next.
Easy, Lee.
Careful.
Yeah, he looks
pretty nasty.
Watch yourself.
I will be fine.
Yeeek!
Uh oh! Is his
cover blown?
It likes him!!!
Wait! It's stabbing him!
I cannot take
anymore...
You know, in a weird way
that was kinda sweet.
Hello, here are your
latte specials.
Ah! And feel free to
take everyone to play
in our little "dog land!"
They can work
on their agility.
Their agility?
It's a fun and
challenging doggy
obstacle course.
They'll love it,
trust me on this
one, okay?
Samehada's definitely
not built for agility.
This might blow his cover!
You're right! That would
say, "it's not a dog"
without actually saying it!
Mhm!
My goodness! There's
a bit of a breeze
out here, isn't there?
He followed us!?
We can't have you
catching a cold,
Samehada.
Oh no, is it too
small? I bought the
largest they had in
the store...
I wonder why it
doesn't fit you.
It doesn't fit because
it's not a dog!!
Look! They've got some
disks to play with!
Wanna fetch, Akamaru?
Aaaroof!
Yay! Good
boy, Akamaru!
Hmph!
[barking sounds]
Oh, uh, did you wanna
catch the disk, too,
Nejimaru?
Eight Trigrams Rotation!
That's weird. Did
you dog just catch
that with his paw?
Ahhhh no of
course not..!
[muffled]
See? He used his mouth
just like any other dog!
Ah, my eyes must
have deceived me.
Okay, Samehada, it's
your turn. Are you
ready?
[freaked out]
[chuckle] You're such
a cute little pup!
(all thinking)
It's not a dog... It's
definitely not a dog..!
Looks yummy! Man,
I want a taste!
Something tells me
things are only
going to get worse.
Akamaru! Find the
buried treasure!
[bark]
I know! I can
use my tail to
help him dig
faster!
Hiiyaa!
[screams]
Hey... Is that
dog's tail actually--
[panicked flailing]
[grunt]
Huh--? Oof!
Just an afterimage!
He's so excited he
was wagging his tail
really fast! See?
I see, it's that
much fun, is it?
Very well. Go on
ahead, Samehada!
[laugh] Take it
easy! That's not a
litter box, silly!
Allow me to explain:
Dogs will sometimes
try to eat kitty litter
because they like to
eat kitty poop.
Even so, that's
not a dog.
Litter, huh?
Don't even think
about it..!
Akamaru! Over here,
boy! Take a look!
[happy barking]
My Taijutsu can
handle this easily!
...Dynamic Drill..!
...Dynamic Jump..!
...Dynamic Wibble-Wobble..!
And finally, to finish
off, my new and improved
version of Dynamic Marking...
Dynamic Marking
Tornado...!
You pig!!
Huh?
Whaaa!?
Akamaru!
woof!
[concerned whine]
[sniffing]
(Narrator)
"Friendship"
Will ya look at
that! You made
a friend, huh?
[happy bark]
Well I'll be! Maybe
we didn't need to be
so focused on finding
a dog friend after all!
(Tobi)
Kisame!
I've been looking
everywhere for you!
Where have you been?
My apologies!
I happened upon this
nice looking dog café
while taking Samehada
out for a walk..!
Hmmm? Dog café..?
But---
Samehada's not
a dog...
He just said it!
What did he say!?
What do you mean
it's not a dog!?
And now you
notice!?
(Waiter)
I'm going to have to
ask all of you to leave
immediately!
Come on!! Can't we
have a happy ending
just once!?
(Narrator)
Oh yeah, I totally
forgot about him...
Huh...
Woof.
(Narrator)
Looks like Rock Lee & team are
taking a quick break on their
way home from today's mission.
[nom nom] These sesame
dumplings are great!
Imagine! Finding a
great tea house out
here!
We should go through
the list of rogue ninja.
Huh?
So, this is
Sasuke's file?
It's been a while
since he left the
Hidden Leaf Village...
...about three years
if I were to guess.
That's right.
Sasuke Uchiha...
He and Naruto were
rivals. And then,
out of nowhere...
A bunch of stuff
happened and he
abandoned the Village!
That exposition
sucked...
Look, we do not
have time to tell
the whole story..
People can go back and
re-watch the main series
if they want to...
Don't mention the
main series!!
Anyway, I wonder what
Sasuke has been up to.
And where has he been?
(Sasuke)
Four lunch
specials, please...
Huh!?
But hold the
natto on mine.
Oh, and four
bottomless sodas,
please.
(Suigetsu)
What? You don't like
natto, Sasuke?
(Sasuke)
Nope. I don't like
natto or sweet things.
(Suigetsu)
Are you bragging!?
-Sasuke!!!!!
"The Shinobi You've
Been Waiting For"
I never expected we'd
run into Sasuke out here.
(Neji)
After all this time,
he just shows up out
of nowhere!
(Lee)
Look at that rope around
his waist. I had no idea he
was such a sucker for trends.
That's the first
thing you notice?!
(Tenten)
Looks like Sasuke
is alone now...
(Lee)
Sasuke..!
It's you three.
Sasuke! Please return
to the Leaf Village!
YOu do not have any
idea how many people
have been worried about
you all this time!
Whatever. Like
I care...
But Sasuke...
...We are having
curry tonight.
Like that makes
a difference!?
Neji!
You are lost, my
friend. Wandering
in the darkness.
So come home, Sasuke.
Also, we're having stew
tonight. Don't be late.
Who cares what kind of
dinner you're having!?
And I'm not a runaway child!
And exactly what kind
of jutsu have you
been learning while
I've been away!?
Hey. Sasuke.
Who're these guys?
Some Leaf ninjas?
Suigetsu!
Who are you? One
of Sasuke's new
companions?
[laugh] That's an
interesting way
to put it...
I just happen to
be traveling with
Sasuke while I peruse
my own goals...
...like the gathering
of a certain set of
swords...
And if you jerks get in
my way, I won't show
any mercy, understand?
What is that!?
It's some kind of
jutsu that turns
his body into water!
Lee, I don't think
your Taijutsu will
work on him.
No problem!
Lightning Style...
Carpet Pad Static
Electricity..!
No! I'm weak against
lightning techniques!
Anything but that..!
But... it's such
a weak attack...
[grunt]
No way! How'd he
take that much damage!?
What have we got
here, Shinobi
from the Leaf?
(Sasuke)
Karin...
Are you exhausted
again already? Man,
you have no stamina!
[laugh] Yeah, sorry.
And this time, it
seems we have a
strong-willed girl
to contend with.
[scoff] Whatever,
loser.
You're not fully
healed yet, either!
Seriously!
Come here...
Oh, Sasuke!
Wh- what' that
girl's deal?
Neji..!
I'm on it!
Byakugan!
I see. That girl
becomes... cuddly
when the glasses
come off!
Nitwit. I could've told
you that without the
Byakugan...
She's a Tsundere!
She acts all haughty
and standoffish, but
the very next moment
she's all lovey-dovey!
What a scary and
confusing technique!
Plus, she wears
glasses...!
It's the ultimate
combination of character
design! A dangerous
masterpiece...!
The woman is
incredible!
Neji! Calm down!
Enough, Karin. Stop
flirting with Sasuke.
Shut up! I
was not!
Why'd she take her
glasses off, anyway?
Come on! Do it!
Just bite my arm
already!
[moaning]
Wh-what was that?
Can we really air
something that
suggestive?
[holding breath]
And you two! Stop
staring so intently,
you perverts!
It, uh, appears to
be a healing technique
where he's sucking
out her chakra!
[gasp] How very
odd...
I suddenly need
more chakra...
Enough! I'm not
letting you bite me!
What's going
on, everyone?
Jugo?
Sorry I'm back
late...
...so, what the birds
told me is true. You've
run into a group of
Leaf ninjas...
Well, so far, so
good. At least this
guy seems normal.
He seems like a
really nice person.
I guess that makes
you the Leaf ninja.
Indeed! You seem like
a reasonable man. Can
we talk to you?
No... I'm
gonna... kill...
What.
...kill you! I'm
gonna kill you!
[laughter]
[scream] What the heck
just happened here!?
Jugo can't control
his emotions. He snaps
at the drop of a hat
out of nowhere...
...It's dissociative
identity.....
I'm gonna [bleep]
your [bleep] up and
shove your hats up
your [bleep]!
That was almost
every single word
you can't say on
the air!!!
It was the same one
Kimimaro used when
I fought him...
What's that?
Kimimaro?
Are you saying that
you knew Kimimaro?
Yes. I was his
final opponent
before he...
passed away.
Is that so...
What were his
last words?
He said...
I just wanna know:
What was the last
thing he ate?
Huh? I-I did not...
At the very end,
what kind of pants
was he wearing!?
What!? Why do you
care about his pants!?
So them, Sasuke,
these are your new
comrades?
Quite a cast of
characters you've
got there. not that
I'm one to talk.
Sasuke. Listen. There is
something I have wanted
to understand for three
years now...
And that is...
to know why..!?
Easy...
Why were you so
popular with all
the ladies!?
Wait, that's
your question!?
Oh, that stuff? I
never cared about it.
[agonizing scream]
Why!? I do not
get it! He does
not even try!!
Lee!
But...I.... I
have....
I have got Sakura
screaming for me all
the time now! That
means something!
(Tenten)
It's not out of
excitement you
moron!
Enough, already.
I've no business
with you.
Please wait...
Just hear me out.
You once considered me
enough of a rival to
copy my moves...
Shut up!
Is that true, Sasuke?
Did you copy his
widdle moves?!
I had my reasons!
Just leave it at that!
It's because they were
so basic. Copying your
movements was nothing
to me...
I have trained a
lot and have
improved since then!
So, do you think
you have what it
takes to copy me
now!?
[scoff]
Wow! He's matching
Lee blow for blow!
How in the world
does he copy him
so fast!?
His Sharingan has
evolved since we
last saw him.
Fine! How about this!
Get a load of my
Sexy Swimsuit Jutsu!
[screaming]
And I am not
done yet!
Behold! The fruits
of my training!
I call this maneuver
the Sexy Swimsuit Special!
Huh!? Why am
I in this!?
Amazing, huh? See
what an incredible
move this is?
Sasuke and I both did
this in the manga,
but your version is
anime-only, Neji!
That doesn't
make it better!
This achievement is the
result of an entire year
of exposure to episodes of
Rock Lee and his Ninja Pals!
Are you kidding!?
Do you know how
many people worked
on this show?!
And the best you can
offer the viewers after
a year is to make Neji
cross-dress? That's sad!
Chidori Stream!!!
It's frustrating,
isn't it...
Snap out of it!
Hurry up and
heal him!
hmf!
Karin!!!
Curse you...
That's enough!
Let's do this!
Suigetsu! Karin!
Jugo! Attack!
No way! Is that--?
It is! A
fusion attack!
Here we come! Combo
ninjutsu! Snake-Hawk
Super Jet!
That combo move
looks... really
stupid.
Brace yourselves!
What the--!?
Where did they
go? They disappeared.
He got us. He trapped
us in an illusion when
we looked at his Sharingan.
There's no telling
how long they've
been gone...
No!!
The cross-dressing,
the stupid combo move...
everything we did!
Sasuke has made fools
of us all! I cannot
believe it!
Last chance, Sasuke.
You're sure of this?
There's no need to
bother with them
any longer. Let's go.
Sasuke? What the--?
Just my luck.
(Narrator)
Looks like everyone
loves that tea house.
(Lee)
The next episode is: "Yamato
gets a Mission" and "Leaf
Village of the Dead!"
(Lee)
You will not want
to miss it!
(Lee)
Sasuke, we are going
back to the village now.
(Sasuke)
I have no intention
of returning.
(Lee)
You pretend to me mad
that you ran into us
at the tea house...
(Lee)
--but you really want
us to accompany you
for a while, right?
(Lee)
You are so immature,
Sasuke!
(Sasuke)
That's not it! I
just... wanted some
of that stew, that's all.
(Tenten)
You sound like a little kid!
Wait, you were listening
during all of that?