This structure is the
Leaf Village's main
government building. It
is in here that Fifth
Hokage, Tsunade, does most
of her work.
Hokage...
What is your opinion on
this matter?
I feel there's only one
way to handle this.
We'll have to overcome
it with hot-blooded
energy!
Whaaat?
Guy Sensei is
the new Hokage.
Wha--? Excuse me, you
said Guy Sensei is the
new Hokage?
How did such a thing
happen?
It's an interim
appointment!
Interim?
Lady Tsunade had to go on
a long international
trip, and she asked Guy
Sensei if he would be
willing to fill in as
Interim Hokage until
she gets back.
Would you please keep
things running smoothly
while I'm gone.
I understand the need,
but why Guy Sensei, of
all people?
Kakashi Sensei and
Shikamaru's father are
off on missions. Guy
Sensei was the only
person at their level who
was free to fill in.
He's always free.
What a great choice! I
know he is going to be
able to handle it.
And we must do everything
in our power to help him
out!
Idiot! Idiot!
Got it! You three want to
help me, is that right?
Anything at all, Sensei!
There's no telling what
kind of craziness Guy
Sensei will get into. And
Lady Tsunade will be
furious if anything
happens while she's
gone.
I am just so moved by
this! To think that our
Guy Sensei is the fill-in
Hokage!
You little fool! I
am no longer Guy Sensei,
I am the Guykage!
Yes! I understand
completely!
Stop making up weird
titles for yourself!
Behold this monument,
Lord Guykage!
Marvel at the beauty of
the great stone faces!
How did all the faces up
there become Guy Sensei?!
I had Captain Yamato
change them with his
wood-style techniques!
Stop dragging innocent
people into your schemes!
Huh? What's this
you've brought me?
These are reports sent
directly to the Guykage.
It is your job to review
them.
Alright, let's see...
This one says morale has
been down among our
ninjas shinobi lately.
Maybe Guy Sensei will
actually bear down and do
the Hokage's job
properly.
Huh?
These stupid fools!
What's wrong?!
It's ridiculous!
How am I supposed to
understand a problem from
one lousy piece of
paper?!
Well first, you'd have
to read it through
completely.
We can't stand by and
let our troubled ninjas
suffer! Let's go, Lee!
Yes sir, Guykage, sir!
Wait, where do you two
think you're going?!
[charging forward]
Hey, ya Pops! One big
order of ramen, please!
Here! Enjoy!
Hey! That was pretty
quick!
Wait a minute. What the
heck is this?
Curried ramen.
Huh?
[chuckling]
Bushier Brow
Sensei?
It's my latest
order as Hokage.
When you're feeling
down, nothing can pick
you up quite like curry.
I heard morale was down,
so I ordered everyone to
start making curry
dishes!
Excuse me? Did you just
say that you're the Hokage?
Guykage to you.
I have to tell you, this
curry is fantastic!
Well it had better be.
Take a look... I went out
and hired a curry expert!
I make the best!
Huh?!
Where did this guy come
from?
Get over yourself,
Naruto, and eat already.
Huh?
Choji?
It's amazing. The curry
ramen is out of this
world! I'm gonna get so
fat eating this.
The truth is, the BBQ
place only had curried
beef today..
And at the Yamanaka
Flower Shop, they only
had curried tulips!
You're kidding! They're
going that far with it?!
So let me see... As long
as I'm here, what else
is it I can do for our
shinobi?
You mean you're not
done?!
Got it!
Idiot! Idiot!
What a great idea! I'll
have all our shinobi wear
my beloved unisuit!
Ahhh!
It is a great idea! They
are sporty, yet
functional!
Excuse me? Naruto?
You mean they got you,
too, Sai?!
Hey! You're not a
shinobi! You're the
last one who should be
wearing that!
Ahhhh! Everyone's
wearing them now!
Time for the Hokage's
next order!
When greeting another
fellow shinobi, you must
give them a hot-blooded
hug!
This will strengthen the
relationships between
shinobi!
Whaat?
Listen, guys! In spite of
what he's saying, you really
don't need to do this!
These are your Hokage's
orders, Naruto! When you
meet a fellow shinobi,
you give them a hug!
What?! I'm telling you,
this is nuts!
Um... Naruto?
Huh?
Well, I guess it can't
be helped. It's the
Hokage's orders.
Huh?
I don't know what's
happening around here.
Where did Lee and Guy
Sensei run off to?
I have no idea.
Hm?
Sorry about all this,
Hinata.
Nuh- Naruto...
[fainting]
Are you alright?!
What's happening here?!
I don't understand! I
didn't do anything!
Hinata?!
Naruto!
Huh--? Neji!
She's passed out! What
exactly is it that you
did to her?!
It wasn't me! It was
the Hokage who ordered---
[screaming]
Wow!
Guy Sensei, you are the
best Hokage I have ever
seen!
Everyone's morale
should be through the
roof by now!
[chuckling]
[angry muttering]
Huh?
This is nuts! We can't
stomach any more of Guy
Sensei being the Hokage!
Captain Yamato! If you do
nothing else, at least
fix Mount Hokage!
They're revolting
against Guykage!
Do not worry. I will take
care of this.
Lee?!
I am the Guykage's
right-hand man. I will be
able to put down this
little rebellion!
Hm?
Please, everyone! It is
important that you calm
down.
I hear your complaints.
Let us talk this out...
Wow! Lee's actually
being serious for a
change!
You may speak
to my fist!
Why am I not surprised?!
We will fight
head-to-head and settle
things, like the true
ninja that we are!
This is your idea of a
peaceful settlement?!
Fine! I accept your
challenge!
But I want to go first!
Human Boulder!
Whoa!
Hey! That always works!
Uh!
Oh!
Okay, Hinata, let's
get moving!
Mm! Ready!
[grunting]
[groaning]
Huh?
Wait a minute... What's
happened to everybody?
I get the feeling
of power...
... like I have a lot more
energy than normal!
That's it! All that
curry I ate has given me
tons of power! That's the
only possible explanation!
I think my Taijutsu
has gone up a level!
Of course! I can move a
lot more freely in these
tights!
It actually
makes sense!
It is unexpected, but
Naruto and I are actually
working well together!
I see it now! That little
hug helped me get used to
being near him!
That move has helped me
open my eyes!
What?!
[groaning]
I thought Bushier Brow
Sensei Hokage's orders
were just his usual
random craziness. But it
turns out they all had a
point!
We didn't understand
what it was! And so we--
Guy Sensei... We can see
now that you really cared
about everyone so much!
Is that honestly
true... Guy Sensei?
Eh?
Oh for heaven's sake!
This idiot didn't give
it any thought at all!
I can't believe it!
Even Captain Yamato is
affected!
Now what?!
Oh no! There are so many
faces of Guy Sensei
appearing, it's getting
freaky!
Huh?!
What the heck?!
The Guy Sensei faces are
all starting to fall on
the village!
What are we gonna do?!
Everything will be
destroyed!
Now don't panic!
We must all band together
and combine our powers to
protect the village!
Yes, Lord Guykage, sir!
Move out!
Hyaaaaah!
Activating Special
Dynamic...
... Entry Attack!
They're all in perfect
harmony?!
We did it! We broke up
every boulder!
Great job,
Lord Guykage!
I apologize, Bushier
Brow Sensei!
You really are
incredible, Guy Sensei!
Congratulations,
Guykage!
Hmm!
Hooray, Guykageee!
You guys are the best!
Alright! Night's coming
on! Let's finish out
the day by running 5000
laps around the
village on our hands!
Yes sir, Guykage, sir!
All you people need to
snap out of it!
Idiot! Idiot!
[sighing]
Thank goodness we're
finally home.
I hope everything went
smoothly while we were
gone.
Huh?!
What's happening here?!
Nothing. We've almost
completed 5000 laps.
It is a motivational
exercise that Lord
Guykage was able to
come up with!
Don't give up now,
everyone! We're almost
there!
What the heck
are you doing?!
I'm building up their
stamina, so they can face
any enemy, no matter who!
[gasping]
You're overdoing it
again! You fool!
I guess Guy Sensei just
wasn't cut out to be
the Hokage.
That may be true.
The bottom line is this.
When examining his
record, you can see that
he is not as cool, calm,
and collected as the
previous Hokages. He is
way too hot-blooded to be
a Hokage, and the reason
is simple. He cannot
ignore the sight of
people suffering right
in front of him.
But that is also the
reason why...
... he is my hero! And
when you get right down
to it, I think he is
every bit as cool as any
Hokage who has ever been!
[chatting]
[growling]
Welcome to the
restaurant!
[growling]
Well, the dishes are
back to normal,
but the ambiance around
here has really changed a
lot, and not for the better.
Let me ask. Do you have a
particular word or phrase
you say a lot?
Okay!
Today's mission is
going to be a patrol
outside the village.
According to what Guy
Sensei told us, there
are rogue ninjas roaming
around,
and causing all kinds
of trouble out in this
area here.
So we're to investigate
these incidents and
report back?
What a drag...
Uh?
Shikamaru?
Hey!
Guess what? Our team's
been assigned to patrol
with you guys.
A total drag, for sure.
Oh, really?
Are you upset? Working
with another squad on
missions is never a bad
thing.
Let us be sure we give
it our all!
A total drag, for sure.
Ugh.
This place is
pretty far away.
It's going to be a long
day, isn't it?
Yeah, and what
a drag.
[sighing]
Shikamaru, will you
please stop saying
everything in the
world is a drag?
Hey, if something's a
drag, it's a drag. There's
no way around it.
Even this
is a drag.
I realize this mission
has the possibility of
being tough,
but your complaining
isn't going to resolve
it. It's only going to
make it worse.
That response is a drag.
What?! Oh, come on!
Easy
Come on, Shikamaru has
been using that phrase
for as long as I can
remember!
However, this is a joint
mission, Shikamaru,
so for the time
being, if you don't
mind, cool it, all right?
I don't know why I
should. In itself, that
would---
[growling]
[sighing]
Which way do we go?
I think the left path is
the shorter one.
It'd still
be a drag...
[growling]
... but we should
take the path on
the right.
Sure about that?
If you feel that
strongly, it must
be the right way!
My gut feeling is that
Shikamaru's super-genius
200 I.Q. will naturally
steer us away from
anything that could be
potentially troublesome.
And as a bonus advantage,
we won't have to listen
to him complaining about
everything.
That's the best
reason of all.
Once the decision was
made, the group headed
down what should have
been a trouble-free path.
However...
Huh?
Oh, Bushy-Brow! This is
perfect! What great
timing you have!You've
arrived re right on time!
Naruto?
We all got together and
decided it was finally
time to try out that new
Kabbadi training you
thought up.
Kabbadi is an Indian
sport. It's a little
different. One of the
rules is, while you're
practicing it, you have
to keep saying "Kabbadi"
over and over until you
run out of
breath.
It's called Kabbadi?
I can say this is
definitely...
... a total drag.
And what's the point of
it, anyway?
Are you ready to join the
fun, Bushy-Brow? If so,
let's hear it for Kabbadi!
Kabbadi!
I am definitely ready!
Kabbadi, Kabbadi,
Kabbadi, Kabbadi!
You don't have to play
it, you know!
Such a total drag,
know what I mean?
Kabbadi, Kabbadi,
Kabbadi, Kabbadi.
Shikamaru, why are you
playing?!
Idiot! Idiot!
Aw, well--we all worked
up a really good sweat!
Anyway, Shikamaru, now
that we look back on it,
it's obvious we should
have taken a left turn
back at that fork
in the road.
No, if we'd taken a
left, we'd have gone
past... a barbecue place
out this way, and Choji
would have been
impossible.
I'm starving to death!
And he would have made
us stop. But as soon as
we walked in...
I'm so sorry. We're
completely out of beef.
But I've got a craving
now! That doesn't work
for me, mister!
You know what would
happen then. We'd be
off to find a cow, out
in the mountains.
There's one!
Hold on, Choji! That's
a female!
Then we'd learn it was
pregnant. And after it
gave birth to its calf,
Choji would be so moved
by the miracle of birth,
that he'd be like...
Hey. I'm gonna live out
here and raise cattle
from now on!
He'd quit his life as a
ninja to become a
rancher...
... and things would
become a real drag.
It makes sense. You
can't argue with that.
Yeah, right! That would
never happen in a
million years!
Alright, that's it!
I've decided I'm gonna
live out here and raise
cattle!
[mooing]
It sounds like someone
out there decided to
become a rancher!
Whaaat?
Another fork in the road.
Oh brother. Which way do
we go?
It's gonna be a
drag, but we should
go left.
Once again, the group
headed down what should
have been a drag-free
path. However...
Huh?
Oh, hey there, Big Bro
Bushy-Brow!
Konohamaru!
You're just in time to
supervise! Our group was
about to start using that
special training method
for sheep-shearing you
came up with a couple of
days ago!
Did he say
"sheep sheering"?
So once again...
... drag's the
correct word.
What do you think is the
"special training
method"?
Why don't you grab some
clippers and join us,
Bushy-Brow?!
That sounds like fun!
Count me in!
I guess I'm in, too.
But it's still a drag!
Why are you
joining in?!
[shivering]
Seriously?
What exactly is going on
here, Shikamaru? I thought
this path was supposed to
be trouble-free?
It was.
If we'd gone right back
there, we'd have passed a
chicken restaurant that's
out this way...
... and Choji would have
been, like...
...I'm starving to
death!
And he would have made
us stop. But then...
I'm sorry, but
we've just run out
of chicken.
Don't do this to me!
Now I've got a craving!
Next thing you know,
we'd be off to find a
chicken, out in the
mountains.
There's one!
Hold on, Choji!
In spite of the crowing,
that's a hen!
Then we would learn that
it was pregnant. And
after its eggs were laid,
Choji would be so moved
by the miracle of birth,
that the next morning,
he'd dedicate his life
to creating a paradise
for chickens.
Things would get really
troublesome.
I can't argue with what
It's a drag.
What's a chicken
paradise, anyway?
I'm going to create a
paradise for chickens!
[crowing]
Apparently, the chickens
have banded together and
support this effort!
Whaat?!
So we've come to
another fork in the road.
It's gonna be a
drag, but... we
should go right.
They hoped the third time
would be the charm.
However...
Glad I caught you, Lee!
The timing couldn't be
more perfect!
As it happens, I'm in
the middle of that new
"politely-refusing-an-
invitation-from-
your-friend-to-go-see-
his-band-perform-live-
at-a-neighborhood-bar"
training that you
came up with.
Who would come up with
training for something
like that?
Just thinking about it
gives me a big headache.
So let's practice, Lee!
As you wish, Guy Sensei!
The first step is to
distance yourself just
enough.
You cannot appear
excited, but you cannot
be repulsed, either.
So then, you smile
slightly uncomfortably--
...And explain why
you simply cannot
participate!
I would love to come, but
unfortunately, I have a
family event that I
absolutely have to
attend that day.
I am so sorry.
What in the world is this
training supposed to
accomplish?!
Such a drag.
Normally I'd be happy
to help, but unfortunately,
I'm cat-sitting for
my uncle while he's
on vacation.
Sorry.
I should have known
you'd buy into this
fantasy! You didn't
even miss a beat!
For the record...
If we'd turned left at
the fork in the road,
we'd have run into
a ramen place...
I'm starving, I
tell you!
But once we walked in...
So sorry, guys, but
we've just run out of
pork.
You can't be serious!
I've got such a craving!
Next thing you know,
we'd be off to find a
pig out in---
That's enough, I get
it. I've heard this
story before.
Alright then, let's
move on. The next step is
what you should do when
someone's insistent and
simply isn't paying
attention.
It's called "Weaseling-
your-way-out-when-you've-
had-the-tickets-forced---
Dammit.
Why is it so important
for us to scramble around
and collect all these
tickets?
Look! A Leaf Ninja!
Didn't expect to see
one of you strolling
around here in the woods!
Come on, boys!
Let's get her!
It had to be now. What a
drag!
Oh my goodness, I'm
starting to sound like
Shikamaru!
You think we're nothing
more than a drag, eh?
Fine, let's rumble!
What?
I would love to, but I
have to be somewhere. So
sorry.
[gasping]
This is ridiculous!
It's the same excuse
people would give me when
I would invite them to
come and see me perform
with my band!
Oh, yeah? It sort of came
out automatically.
In the past, whenever
I'd invite someone to
come and see us, they'd
make that face and
politely refuse. Not one
single person showed up!
Huh?
How dare you hurt our
friend's feelings like
that?!
Wait...
It wasn't on purpose,
I assure you.
Huh?
[sneezing]
I can't believe it!
This is wool!
What the--? How could
you possibly know I was
allergic to wool?!
Huh?! It's a
surprise to me!
Wait a minute.
Is it possible? Did
Shikamaru research the
rogue ninjas before the
mission, learn their weak
points, then lead us down
these troublesome paths
so we could engage and
overcome them?
I have to give you
credit, young lady.
You're quite the ninja,
to have figured out both
my friends' weak
points.
But I bet you can't
figure out how to beat
me, can you?
Heh! Please, your weak
point couldn't be more
obvious.
Let's see how you
handle this!
Kabbadi! Kabbadi!
What was that all about?
That didn't tap
your weakness?!
Seems like Kabbadi had
nothing to do with
anything.
Well, whatever that
was all about, now
it's my turn!!
What the hell? Why
can't I move?
Huh?
This is such a drag!
Shikamaru?
Tenten!
You alright?!
[grunting]
Now I realize that
Shikamaru predicted this
from the beginning. He
could have saved us a lot
of trouble if he had just
explained it to start with.
Hm?
Oh, it's nothing.
Never mind.
Good heavens, this is
truly a drag..
Yeah, you can be such a
drag, all right.
Hey, Tenten!
Now that those rogue
ninjas are under control
and we have some time,
let us practice the
"Indescribable-anger-when-
you-finally-go-to-see-the-
band-but-find-out-there's-
a-separate-charge-for-
the-drinks" training!
Oh boy. You, my friend,
are such a drag!
Next time is
"Infiltrate Akatsuki's
Hideout" and "A Desperate
Escape Plan"!
But guess what? We're
not participating in the
episode.
Let me guess... it's
because it's such a
drag, right?
That's not it.
Huh?
If we were to be in the
episode, Choji would get
hungry and go to a sushi
restaurant
only to find that they
were out of mackerel.
And then, he would--
Are you starting up with
that again? I thought we
were done after covering
all the meats!
But now, you're
on to fish?!