Caring for pets can be a
lot of fun. Millions of
people do it every day.
But when it comes to the
animals used by ninjas,
things aren't always so
simple.
This mission I'm on
came out of nowhere. Would
you mind entertaining these
two until I get back?
Sure thing!
And I can tell you right
now, they will be in good
hands!
The Fifth Hokage needs me
to do something for her. I
was wondering if you could
watch my animals for me.
Certainly, my friend!
I'll treat them better
than at any kennel you
could take them to.
I hate to ask this, but
could you watch Tonton
for me for a couple of
days? And Katsuyu as
well, just to be on the
safe side?
Oh please, don't even
give it a second thought!
I'd be happy to do it!
Caring for Animals
is Hard Work!
[gasping]
I can't believe we have
so many pets to look
after.
Yeah, I hope we can
handle it.
Heh-heh. Don't
worry yourselves.
In fact...
I'm adding my ninja
tortoise to the mix!
We have enough
on our plates!
We don't need a
tortoise as well.
You got a problem,
young lady?!
Allow me to remind
you, I've been watching
out for you brats since
you were genin!
He's right. For us
ninjas, our animals are
some of our most reliable
allies!
Yes, but since I am a
shinobi who cannot use
ninjutsu
have the skills to properly
care for a pack of ninja
hounds, let alone other
summoned animals.
Don't be absurd! Just
ignite your youthful
passion, and you can form
a bond with any animal!
Idiot! Idiot!
All right...
Gamakichi and
Gamatastsu...
Sup?
Katsuyu and Tonton...
Oink.
Kakashi Sensei's eight
ninja hounds...
Pakkun...
Hi.
Bull, Shiba...
Yo.
Biscuit...
Hey.
Guruko...
Hi.
Uhashi...
Sup?
Akino...
Yeah.
Uhei!
Right.
Yahooo!
There goes Kiba and
Akamaru.
Akamaru! Dynamic Marking!
[barking]
Hey, watch where you're
spraying, alright?!
Wow! What great
technique!
I have to agree. A
perfect demonstration!
Seriously, the dogs are
really impressed! Is the
move that wonderful?
It... looks like
so much fun.
I know you, Guy Sensei!
Don't you dare attempt
that one!
Hey there! What are you
guys up to?
By sheer coincidence,
everybody on our team is
animal-sitting for
someone this week!
Oh...
That means we'll all be
best friends in no time!
[struggling]
Ah yes, bonding through
kinship! It happens so
much, it's a normal
part of youth!
Right, Guy Sensei!
That would be fine,
except the animal clearly
hates it!
[growling]
Look, Guy Sensei! Akamaru
is playing with me! Is that
not wonderful?
Great job, Lee! You and
Akamaru have formed an
unbreakable bond!
I seriously doubt
that. Oh, boy.
You're a bad dog,
Akamaru.
[whimpering]
Well, it's clear. You
and Akamaru understand
each other, don't you,
Kiba?
We should. We've been
inseparable since we were
both babies.
He's very different
from a summoned animal.
For those who don't
know, summonings,
like Kakashi Sensei's
dogs, normally live
somewhere far away. But
they're always on
alert, and immediately
come to the aid of their
summoner when they're
called upon.
Wait! In that case...
We don't need anyone
to take care of us.
Oh, I beg to differ!
We promised to use our
full powers to care for
you!
You're always so
stubborn about things
like this.
Fine, then...
Scatter!
[gasping]
They ran off!
Hmpf! If you want to
watch us so badly, you'll
have to catch us, first.
But take heed! The great
Pakkun will not be caught
so easily!
Don't be such a smug
pug!
Hey, this is cool, bro!
It's just like playing
tag!
Except we have a head
start!
[oinking]
Stop, Akamaru!
What the heck? Everyone
took off and ran away.
Even Katsuyu!
Pop quiz for
everybody!
Think about it carefully.
What shocking action did
the animals just take?
We already know the
answer to that one! The
question is, what are we
gonna do?!
It is obvious!
We have to go out there
and catch them all, and
give them the best care
on earth!
[panting]
All this running is
making me hungry, bro.
We need to stop somewhere
and get ourselves a snack!
No way! You'll just
have to suck it up
'til we're clear!
Really?
Huh?
Mmm.
Yummyyyy!
Gamatastsu, that's not
a snack! That's Tonton,
and you have to put her
down now!
Sorry, my friend, but I
suddenly had a craving
for pork!
You have to control
yourself!
Ah, there you are!
You're coming back!
Tonton! Katsuyu! Thank
goodness we found you!
Hold on!
Don't touch him!
Thanks, bro!
Back off! I won't let
you hurt my brother! He
didn't mean any harm!
Don't try to
cover for him.
Just hear me out.
You must know what it's
like, sometimes. You've
got that cousin, don't you?
Her name is Hinata,
if I recall.
Truthfully, you'd
protect Hinata if she
got herself in trouble,
wouldn't you?
Mm.
[trembling]
I'm here, Hinata!
Of course I would.
And more to the point, if
Hinata wanted to eat some
flies, you'd catch them
for her, wouldn't you?
Uh!
All that running made me
really hungry!
Help yourself, Hinata! I
was able to catch a lot
for you!
That would never happen!
I'm not done!
Don't forget about her
big, scary dad,
Hinabunta!
I'm Hinata, folks!
Hinabunta? What are you
even talking about?!
Plus, I haven't even
mentioned Hinahiro and
Hinaken.
Sorry. But I'm very
clumsy.
How many types of Hinatas
do you think there are?!
A lot. And they all live
on Mount Hinaboku,
don't they?
Mount Hinaboku?!
So, under these
circumstances,
I'm sure you can--
Not in the slightest,
big-mouth!
Uh!
Oiiiink.
Tonton?
What are you doing?
Gamatastsu was one step
away from eating you! And
you'd still protect him?
Oink.
Oink. Oink, oink. Oink,
oink.
She's obviously saying
something important, but
I can't understand a
single word!
Oh, well.
Whatever.
You're safe now!
Oink!
Hold it!
Stop running, right now!
Why do I feel like
we're being chased,
along with everyone else?
[whimpering]
All right, you guys! You
asked for it!
Fanged Pursuit Jutsu!
How do you like this? The
hunter's become the
hunted. You're really
stuck now, Guy.
Awww.
You finally decided to
play with me!
You're mis-interpreting
what's going on here.
Guy Sensei!
Look at this! Kiba and
Akamaru have decided to
play with me!
And from the looks of it,
they're both having a
lot of fun!
For heaven's sake! Are
the two of you guys
really that crazy?
Guy Sensei, do you want
to trade your dogs for my
Fang-Over-Fang?
You... don't
mind?
What in the world is
happening here?
Well, that tears it!
Akamaru! Everyone! It's
time for our special
attack!
A combo attack with all
nine dogs?!
Wow!
Hyper Dynamic Marking!
Please, this craziness
has to stop!
[grunting]
So gross!
Akamaru, combo
transformation!
[barking]
A two-headed wolf?!
When Kiba and Akamaru do
a combined transformation,
this is how they end up.
Now I have got you!
Stop, Lee! You
don't know--ah!
[grunting]
What happened here?!
He got mixed in! Lee,
Kiba and Akamaru are
doing a combo move!
This is actually a pretty
cool deal, huh?
What are you talking
about?! Dude, we couldn't
look less cool!
We gotta run for it!
Wait for us!
Hold it!
Huh?
Come on, how's a
tortoise supposed
to catch us?
My ninja tortoise is faster
than any rabbit, or dog,
for that matter!
What?! Wait a second!
Collabo Taijutsu!
Tortoise Power!
[screaming]
That tortoise is
really fast!
[gasping]
You overdid it, Guy
Sensei! It was too much!
[gasping]
[groaning]
Huh?
So... Is everybody
alright?
[whimpering]
[chuckling]
Interesting. I see he
managed to get out of the
combo in time to save the
dog.
[chuckling]
Nice work, dude.
Hey, thanks a million,
guys.
Looking back, we ended up
having a lot of fun!
Looks like it's
mission accomplished.
But still... we have
quite a ways to go.
Next time this kind of
thing happens... I will
ignite my youthful fires
and truly learn to
understand the animals!
You know something, Lee?
I believe you!
Lee and his pals swore to
learn from their experience
and do better the next time.
And...
It turned out they got
that chance sooner than
they expected.
Here are our new charges!
You're nuts! Forget
about it!
It's starting to get
chilly out here in the
Hidden Leaf Village.
So... is everybody
ready for winter?
Maybe we should all do
some joint training, once
in a while.
Good idea! We should go
find Hinata.
Hold on! Isn't that her
right there?
Hm?
Maybe it is me, but she
seems sad.
Oh, it's not anything
real big...
It's just the change in
seasons. Winter's almost
here and it's got me
feeling kinda down.
What's wrong with winter?
There's lots of fun stuff
about to come up.
There's the whole
Christmas thing, and
New Years...
The first temple visit,
Valentine's Day...
I get it. These are all
days best enjoyed by
couples.
You'd like to spend
them with Naruto,
wouldn't you?
[gasping]
Is that what this is
about, Hinata?
Mmmm, well--
It would make me happier
if I could just get a little
bit closer to him, you know?
But I don't think I'm
ever going to get that
chance.
Come on, winter hasn't
even started yet.
We can arrange for all
the chances you need.
It will be our mission as
a group to make sure you
spend winter with a smile
on your face!
Yeah, we're all
onboard!
[affirmative barking]
Thank you!
Neji?
Fine, I'm in.
Heh!
Howl at Naruto!
We have tried going on
the offensive before and
have failed miserably.
Now we will do the
opposite. And try to make
things feel as natural as
possible.
What do you have in mind,
specifically?
Something like...
[gasping]
Naruto!
Thanks for letting me
borrow it.
What's this one?
I thought since you
liked the first book,
you'd like this, too!
Thanks, and next time,
I'll loan you some more
of my favorites!
Trading books back and
forth will start to close
the gap, and then, when
Christmas rolls around...
... she can up the ante
with a handmade scarf! If
that does not get to him,
nothing will!
Isn't that a
bit too dull?
No. I think it has a nice
flow to it.
So what do you think,
Hinata?
I think I can pull it off
so it feels natural.
Then it is settled! The
game is afoot, everyone!
We are standing by. What
is the situation?
I'm on Fourth Street. I
can report the target is
on the move and approaching
your location. Over.
Thanks, that is excellent
news! Time to get in
position, Hinata.
Right!
I wonder if this will
work.
I still have eyes on
target. He's closing in
fast. Oh!
Something wrong?
He's passing by the
library. I think he must
be headed to the shopping
mall.
He's probably heading
to Ichiraku.
Yeah.
[sighing]
This is incredibly
frustrating! I mean, we
were so close!
Hey, admit it, you were
way off. I mean, Naruto's
probably never set foot
in a library before.
You have a good point.
I guess my idea was a
complete failure.
That's a shame.
We got nowhere.
I refuse to accept that.
We just need to bring
Naruto here in a way that
is both natural and casual.
So your idea is...
By pure coincidence, we
just happen to run into
him while we're out on
the town...
And that's what you
call "natural"?!
Okay, here is another
thought.
We could hire a
detective to grab Naruto
and bring him here in a
most natural way!
Sorry Lee, but I'm
afraid you're missing
the point again.
Howl at the Sunset.
Our plan will not work
any other way. Do you
understand, Meatball-Head?
Meatball Head? Are you
talking to me?
A detective always gives
his underlings nicknames.
Cool! So what's mine?
You are "Mittens" and
Akamaru is "Boots".
All right! We've
been given dog names!
Those happen to be cat
names.
Well in our home, we
don't discriminate!
The cats are happy to
hear that!
Hmpf! This is dumb!
Neji's referred to
as "Big Sis".
Wait a minute! What do
you mean "Sis"?!
No insubordination, or
you will be fired. Let us
roll!
Wait, everybody.
You've forgotten
something critical.
And what would that be,
exactly?
Well, my nickname.
What?! And why is your
nickname critical?
How can you ask that?
If I don't have a
nickname, it will hinder
our ability to complete
the mission.
Forg O'ten will be
your new name!
Forg... O'ten?
Forgotten?
How in the world... did
this happen?
Forg, are you all right?!
This is all my fault! I
let my poor subordinate
get killed in the line of
duty!
He wasn't exactly
killed in action, since
you pulled the trigger
yourself!
His sacrifice will not be
in vain! Let us roll out!
You're all going? What
am I supposed to do?
Wait inside until we get
back. We will bring the
suspect to you!
Uh...
What a meal! Man, am I
ever stuffed! I have the
time, so I guess I'll go
see what Sakura's up to.
Forget it! You're not
getting past me!
What's your problem?
You're a suspect in the
legendary Amano River
murders, where you were
able to use the ol'
perfectly timed-gluttonous
maid-finds-the-melon-bread-
dripping-with-blood trick!
You're comin'
with me!
I don't know what you
mean!
This will be easier on
everybody if you come
quietly!
[grunting]
Sorry, but you're not
making any sense!
The perp's running!
Do not worry. Those two
guys are expert trackers.
They will not let him get
away.
Attaboy!
Nobody ever escapes from
our noses! Huh? That
smells like---
You're sure these are
good?
Just have yourself a
bite! I know they smell
awful, but they taste
great!
Why are you grilling
salted horse mackerels?!
You okay?
They've looked better,
that's for sure.
Mittens! Boots! Are you
there? Respond!
Howl at the Sunset.
Their sense of smell
betrayed them.
What's happening out
there?
We lost Mittens and
Boots! But we will track
the man down and get him
next time, I swear!
Oh... Okay.
Looks like I was finally
able to lose them.
But what was that all
about? Huh?
There she is!
Sakura, where are you
headed? I finally found
you!
Eight Trigrams Air Palm!
I don't care if it does
trap the suspect, this
outfit is just way too
much.
Neji, is Naruto okay?!
Generally, yes, although
I may have overdone it
just a little.
What?!
Who are you talking to?
And... what's going on
with you people today?!
None of your business,
but I've got you now!
Mission accomplished!
What the heck is my crime
here? Am I being detained
just because I mistook
the cross-dressing
pervert, Neji, for the
real Sakura?
Did you say
cross-dressing
pervert?
Pervert?
Eww.
Stay back, don't go
near him!
Wait! Why am I in the
line of fire?!
This is all wrong!
I have to talk--
Farewell, Big Sis.
Howl at the Sunset.
So Big Sis is out?
We have no options.
We have to take him
by force.
No! You can't
do that!
This whole process was
supposed to feel natural!
Listen, Hinata!
This is no longer going
down at the library! It
will be at the scene of
the crime!
Uhh... Why are you
Detective Lee Aojima?
You're supposed to be
Chief Leejiro!
Uh!
What should I do?
Freeze right there!
I said "freeze",
sucker! Why are you
running?!
I'm running 'cause you're
chasing me! And whatever
it is, I didn't do it!
[grunting]
This should shake her,
once and for all.
[grunting]
What the---?!
End of the line, mister!
What?! Now you've
become Daimon?! You've
gotta stop changing
characters!
All right, that's it!
I'm taking you out!
You have no chance!
[grunting with anger]
Bring it!
[gasping]
Protective Eight
Trigrams!
Huh?! Whoa!
Thank goodness I got here
in time!
Hinata! Ruuunnn!
[screaming]
Ahhhhh!
Hinata! Are
you all right?
Naruto?
I'm so sorry. I guess
I just got in the way.
I need to get you to a
hospital. Don't try
and talk!
Are you...
all right?
If I didn't mention
it... Thank you for
saving me.
Mmm.
What does
this mean?
I don't know how these
things happen, but all's
well that ends well, right?
And so, in spite of some
unexpected turns along
the way,
Hinata was able to
get a little closer
to Naruto. However...
It'll be about a month
before you're fully
healed.
Really. It's that
serious? A whole month?
Don't you worry.
Rest up and we'll have you
out of here just before
New Year's!
[gasping]
Believe me, you haven't
lived until you experience
the joy of spending Christmas
in a hospital bed.
Next time: "Tenten vs.
Temari" and "Orochimaru's
Search for Love"!
Oh, really?
You are not curious? Even
Orochimaru wants to get
married!
You and the other
sensei's should think
about settling down
as well!
I'm... more interested
in reading the final
book in the "Make-Out
Tactics" series.
Uh, yeah. I'm too busy
with my training. I
really have no time
to date.
I hear those are common
excuses from men who are
too old to find a partner.
Hey, I resemble that!