NARRATOR: In the beginning,
when the universe was born,
there was only Demiurge,
the soulless creator,
the true form of the idea.
It was alone
amid a chaos of shapeless souls.
Demiurge did not know of the existence
that had created it.
It did not know of the existence of souls.
[ Whooshing ]
It did not know of the idea
the world it created
was merely a shadow of the real world.
[ Chiming ]
[ Cracking ]
[ Whooshing ]
[ Alarm clock beeping ]
[ Tai grunting ]
[ Click, alarm stopping ]
[ Car engines rumbling ]
WOMAN: Authorities are investigating
a series of mysterious power outages
that have been happening in factories
throughout the region.
[ Rumbling ]
KARI: Tai!
Get up, Tai!
TAI: Oh, man.
KARI: You awake?
[ Rumbling ]
Of course not.
Hello? World to Tai Kamiya, wake up.
Let's go, rise and shine!
You're gonna be late for soccer practice
if you don't get up.
TAI: What? Oh, no!
[ Rumbling ]
Bye, mom. Bye, sis.
A \"thank you\" would be nice.
[ Door closing ]
[ Lightning crashing ]
[ Music playing ]
MAN: ♪ Digimon, digi, digi, Digimon ♪
♪ Di, di, di ♪
♪ Di, di, Digimon ♪
♪ Di, di, di, di ♪
♪ Digimon, digi, digi, Digimon ♪
♪ Di, di, di ♪
♪ It's Digitime again ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon, digital champions ♪
♪ Digimon, Digimon, Every day ♪
♪ Digimon, digi, digi, Digimon ♪
♪ Digi, Digimon ♪
♪ Fighting to save the Earth ♪
♪ As only they can ♪
♪ Digimon, Digimon ♪
♪ Adventures in the digital world ♪
♪ The Ultimate Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon, digi, digi, Digimon ♪
♪ Digi, Digimon ♪
♪ Di, di, Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon digital monsters, Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon, digital champions ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon ♪
♪ Di, Digimon, Digimon back again ♪
♪ Digimon back again ♪
MAN: There it goes.
MAN: I got it. I got it.
MAN: Over here.
MAN: Whoo!
[ Music playing ]
MAN: ♪ Digi, Digimon ♪
♪ Di, di ♪
♪ Digi, Digimon ♪
♪ Di, Digimon ♪
Ready, guys?
MAN: Ready for what? We're done.
Yeah, the only thing I'm ready for is a break.
Quitters.
Hmm.
Hmm?
Kari, what are you doing here?
Hello? Forgot your lunch.
Oh, wow, thanks a lot.
Don't worry, you'll make it up to me.
You can repay me
with a super jumbo chocolate strawberry
tropical thunder bucket.
Fine, fine.
Whatever you say.
MAN: Come on, Tai, get off your butt
and get back to work.
TAI: What? I thought you guys said you wanted a break.
MAN: Break time's over.
We got a big match coming up, remember?
Hey, you gonna come cheer us on, Kari?
What?
Oh? Sure. Yeah.
At least, I sure hope I can.
MAN: You better.
MAN: ♪ Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon digital champions ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon ♪
♪ Di, Digimon Digimon back again ♪
It's this coming Sunday?
That's right.
SORA: Hmm.
Oh, hey, Tai.
MATT: Hey...
What's up?
TAI: Hmm?
Am I interrupting?
Hey, Tai.
-What's the word? -TAI: Morning, Mr. Nishijima.
DAIGO: So, uh, did you finish it yet or not?
TAI: Uh, not quite.
Sorry.
Everyone else has turned theirs in.
Oh, man.
Well, I wanna see you in my office after lunch.
-Right. -DAIGO: Hey, I mean it.
Yes, sir. Right. I'll be there, don't worry.
DAIGO: You'd better be.
SORA: What was all that?
TAI: I forgot to do my list of future goals.
What? You still haven't finished it?
[ Music playing ]
MATT: Just make some decisions
and get it over with, dude.
TAI: Yeah, yeah.
[ Electricity buzzing ]
[ Indistinct chatter ]
[ Music playing ]
MAN: Yes, please.
MAN: Oh, sure.
MAN: Can I have one of those?
Hmm?
You wanna come?
We're playing a gig.
TAI: Huh, you still with the Teenage Wolves?
MATT: Nah, that band broke up.
This is a new band.
Knife of Day.
[ Glass shattering ]
[ Tai chuckling ]
Catchy name.
Why'd the Wolves break up anyway?
I don't know, creative differences, I guess.
[ Laughing ]
Creative, you?
[ Grunting ]
Watch it, will you?
You gonna make me hurl my combo bowl.
Wait, it's on Sunday?
Sorry, I've got a soccer game.
MATT: Okay. Never mind.
Forget it, then.
Can you pass the pepper?
TAI: Sure.
Hey, knock it off.
TAI: No problem. Just trying to help out.
-Get away. -Geez.
You're trying to ruin it or something?
Maybe you put that much pepper on your ramen,
but that's because you've got no taste.
I guess we have creative differences.
MATT: Zip it.
DAIGO: So, what are your goals, Tai?
What is it you wanna do with your future?
You must have thought about it.
TAI: About my future?
Not really.
DAIGO: Hey!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Was this yours, Mr. Nishijima?
Not anymore, it's not.
Go on, finish it.
Thanks. You're awesome.
DAIGO: Anyway...
Think.
There must be something you wanna do.
Well, I don't really know.
DAIGO: You can't think of one thing?
TAI: Well, okay. Yeah.
I'd like to see an old friend again.
I used to see him a lot.
But he lives really far away,
in a place that's not easy to get to.
Friend in a foreign country.
Yeah.
Something like that.
DAIGO: Well, if you're interested in traveling,
what about studying a foreign language?
There are a lot of good schools for that.
At least, it would get you started
in a good direction.
Uh-huh.
Just remember,
dream big.
[ Electronic buzzing ]
[ Music playing ]
[ Insectlike clattering ]
[ Wings fluttering ]
Huh?
[ Whooshing ]
MAN: All these-- all that?
You know, I totally did it all already.
Yeah.
[ Ball thudding ]
TAI: Hey, Izzy?
Got a second?
IZZY: Sorry, Tai,
Sunday is my parents' anniversary,
and we always celebrate by going out to dinner.
TAI: Oh, I get it.
You can't miss that.
IZZY: Is everybody else going?
TAI: Matt's band is playing a gig.
That means T.K. probably won't be able to come, either.
And Joe's got to study for his entrance exams,
but Kari might show.
It's not easy getting everyone together anymore, is it?
Don't worry about it.
It's not like it's a big deal.
I just thought if you weren't doing anything,
-you know... -I got an idea.
Why don't we try texting Mimi?
Maybe she can go.
Right.
Mimi's in New York City,
like she's just gonna hop on a plane.
IZZY: That's the thing, you'll never know with Mimi,
she's very unpredictable.
TAI: I wonder how she's doing, anyway.
Whoa, she already wrote back. Look.
MIMI: Hi, thanks for the invite.
I'd love to.
I'll go ahead and book the flight.
You can pay me back.
Can't wait to see you guys.
What?
-She's coming? -IZZY: Apparently.
Let's check out some flights.
It looks like you can't get anything this weekend for...
under a thousand dollars.
See? Look at these fares.
And that's not including baggage fees,
and you know Mimi,
I'm sure she never travels
with less than three or four suitcases.
And it has to be a direct flight with no layovers,
or she'll miss your game.
And, knowing Mimi,
she is definitely going to want a seat in first class.
TAI: Let's forget it.
T.K.: Sorry, I've already got plans on Sunday.
KARI: Oh, so you can't come?
T.K.: Nah, I'm taking a friend to see my brother's band.
KARI: Is this friend a she?
T.K.: Yeah.
I see.
So it's kind of like a date, huh?
T.K.: No, it's not like that.
She's a friend, that's all.
KARI: Mm-hmm.
T.K.: What does that mean?
Hmm, nothing.
Wait a second.
Hey, you're not jealous, are you?
[ Chuckling ]
KARI: Yeah, right.
But I am worried that Tai's gonna be pretty bummed
if nobody's there to cheer him on.
Yeah, same with Matt,
he was really hoping everyone would come to his gig.
He said that?
Nah, of course he didn't.
He's just like Tai,
they pretend they don't care, but we know what's going on.
KARI: Yeah.
Look, I'll come next time, okay?
Sure, see you later.
Bye.
[ Wind blowing ]
[ Electronic buzzing ]
[ Gasping ]
MAN: Okay, don't get too comfortable,
because I have the results of the practice exam,
and I'm now going to assign everyone's seats
according to how they did.
So if you all would please stand up.
The first row's for those who got an A,
the second row's for B's,
third's for C's, etcetera.
If you're in the fourth row or farther,
you need to buckle down.
JOE: Oh, the fourth row? That's me.
Sorry, Matt.
Can't make the show on Sunday, wish I could.
Got to study every weekend for the rest of my life,
hope you understand.
[ Sighing ]
WOMAN: Same here, we're starting to get a lot
of sightings coming in.
DAIGO: I see.
WOMAN: The effects have been minimal so far,
but it's only a matter of time.
[ Buzzing ]
DAIGO: Understood.
I'll continue to monitor the situation on my end and...
[ Beeping ]
WOMAN: Lost him.
Hmm...
[ Music playing ]
WOMAN: Turning now to local news and today's top story.
Sorry, Tai,
gonna have to miss your game.
Yeah.
It's no biggie.
I wouldn't expect you to skip your friend's birthday party.
-Hmm. -WOMAN: ...but that is all
they're willing to say at this time.
So far, no one has been able
to determine the cause of these mysterious power failures.
Scientists at the National Institute of Astro...
Hey, Tai?
I'm fine with it.
So everyone's too busy to come.
It's not like it's the end of the world.
So you're not the least bit disappointed?
-I don't care. -You care.
You care a lot.
It's okay, you can admit you're bummed.
I'm not bummed. Let's just drop it.
I'm out of here.
Oh, wait, that news story, did you hear it?
They're refreshingly sweet, good-for-you treat.
News story?
KARI: Never mind.
It's nothing.
Hey, have a great game.
[ Music playing ]
TAI: Sora, just wondering,
are you going to Matt's gig tonight?
[ Phone buzzing ]
SORA: Why? What's up?
TAI: I've got a soccer game,
city field, 2:00.
No big deal, if you can make it, that'd be great.
MAN: Sorry, can you get by?
We'll be out of here in a minute.
[ Music playing ]
SORA: Can't believe that Tai.
Why couldn't he have told me sooner?
Now I have to find an outfit that works for both.
Let's see.
His game starts at 2:00,
but it'll take me at least 30 minutes
to get ready and get to Matt's show.
Oh.
What should I do?
Okay, let's see.
Maybe, if I leave as soon as the game's over,
of course, that all depends on when Matt's band comes on,
it'd just be my luck they play first,
and I miss the whole set.
The game could end early.
This is driving me crazy.
Why'd they both have to be today?
Wait a minute.
Why am I getting upset?
It's their problem, not mine.
Yeah, forget it.
I'll just skip 'em both, that's what I'll do.
Oh, man, who am I kidding?
I got to get moving.
What's going on?
[ Beeping ]
Hey, that's my lucky number.
What am I doing? I've got to get going!
Oops, forgot my phone.
[ Music playing ]
[ Buzzing ]
Oh, excuse me a second.
-Hello? -SORA: It's me, sorry.
Am I interrupting?
-Sora? -You got a minute?
I could use some advice.
IZZY: Sure, ask away.
I'm just... working in the computer lab.
What's up?
I've got kind of a situation.
A situation, huh?
I see, just a second.
[ Speaks French ]
Uh... I think something's wrong with the phone.
That sounded like French.
Maybe the lines are crossed or--
IZZY: There have been a lot of problems
with communications lately.
You've heard about all these power surges
and blackouts they've been having, haven't you?
[ Speaks French ]
-Hmm? -IZZY: [ Speaks French ]
Forget it.
It's no use.
I can't make out half of what you're saying.
I'll try you later.
No. Sora, wait.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Sound check starting ]
T.K.: Well, sell a lot of tickets?
Bet you did, 'cause everybody I know
is dying to hear your new band.
I love the name,
the, uh-- wait, sorry,
what's the name of the band again?
We're called Knife of Day.
[ Static ]
Whoa.
That's weird.
Huh?
Hmm.
What the heck is going on?
That's not what I typed.
[ Wings fluttering ]
WOMAN: Okay, see you later.
WOMAN: Bye.
MAN: So what's the deal with Kari?
I thought you said she was coming, Tai.
I thought she was,
but then something else came up.
Huh?
MAN: What is that thing?
WOMAN: Oh, my gosh.
Look out!
-MAN: Hey, where are you going? -TAI: Got to run, guys.
What happened?
Hello?
Are you still there?
WOMAN: What's going on?
You got no service.
WOMAN: Mommy, look, it stopped working...
[ Music playing ]
MAN: Hey, what's the holdup?
MAN: Come on, this is nuts.
MAN: Move it. Get out.
MAN: Stop yelling at me.
[ Music playing ]
[ Wings fluttering ]
What's Kuwagamon doing here?
WOMAN: Until the end of the month,
but returning to our top story,
we have breaking news just coming in.
Eyewitness footage shows
a large unidentified creature or machine
hovering over the downtown area,
at the same time
as malfunctioning traffic lights
have brought traffic there to a standstill,
and communications
continue to be affected.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
I'm thinking so.
Oh, hey,
about Matt's gig today,
I think it's just been cancelled.
Sorry about that.
Yeah, another time.
A girlfriend?
Well, she's a girl, that's for sure,
but don't worry about it,
nobody will ever come between us, brother.
Yeah, whatever.
Huh?
That's weird,
Tai's not answering.
He's probably playing soccer.
Oh, hey, hi.
So, uh, you know my brother's gig tonight?
[ Music playing ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Wings fluttering ]
[ Glass breaking ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Glass shattering ]
[ Crashing ]
Kuwagamon?
[ Music playing ]
[ Screaming, shouting ]
[ Speaks French ]
[ Wings fluttering ]
Not this again.
Really? I can't believe it.
Why is this suddenly happening?
[ Electronic buzzing ]
Whoa.
JOE: Hey, what's going on?
Of course, my computer would decide to break today.
Oh.
I'll never finish this report.
Maybe I'm just destined to fail.
SORA: That's weird, I think my watch stopped.
Hmm.
And my phone says the wrong time, too.
WOMAN: Oh, that's-- that's strange.
Are you-- are you getting a signal?
MAN: No. Nothing.
WOMAN: Hey, what's that?
Did you see it?
[ Indistinct chatter ]
There you are.
[ Music playing ]
[ Electronic buzzing ]
[ Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Crashing ]
TAI: This is no random attack.
Kuwagamon's definitely after me.
But why?
[ Crashing, grunting ]
[ Wings fluttering ]
Whoa.
[ Crashing ]
[ Growling ]
[ Wings fluttering ]
[ Crashing ]
[ Growling ]
Look at all the damage he's already done.
And you know who's gonna get blamed for it,
the good Digimon.
But what can I do?
[ Growling ]
What are you doing here?
[ Crashing ]
[ Wings fluttering ]
I have to do something.
I've got to stop him before he hurts somebody.
Maybe I can lead him away from the city.
[ Wings fluttering ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Crashing ]
[ Grunting ]
Huh?
[ Music playing ]
TAI: I can't stop him...
[ Roaring ]
by myself.
I can't do anything.
[ Growling ]
[ Whooshing ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Growling ]
[ Crashing ]
Huh?
No way!
Hey, Tai.
Agumon!
I can't believe it's really you.
It's me.
But you got bigger, Tai.
Are you sure it's not 'cause you shrank?
Hmm, still work to do.
[ Growling ]
Agumon, let's take this monster out.
Heard that.
[ Music playing ]
Agumon digivolve to...
MAN: [ Singing in Japanese ]
...Greymon!
[ Roaring ]
MAN: [ Singing in Japanese ]
[ Growling ]
[ Roaring ]
Kuwagamon is a lot stronger than he was
the last time we fought.
Is it a problem?
Nah. I can still take him.
All right. Do it.
GREYMON: [ Growling ]
MAN: [ Singing in Japanese ]
TAI: Huh?
They vanished.
MAN: [ Singing in Japanese ]
[ Growling ]
[ Electronic buzzing ]
[ Crashing ]
[ Rumbling ]
[ Electronic buzzing ]
TAI: Greymon! Hey!
Where are you, Greymon?
[ Phone vibrating ]
Hmm?
What's up, Kari?
KARI: Tai, we've got trouble.
I think you need to get out to the airport.
WOMAN: All flights out of International Airport
have been cancelled.
To the airport?
Well, at the moment, that could be a slight problem.
All right.
I'll start-- Wait.
KARI: What did you say?
- Tai? -Nothing.
Thanks for the call. I'll get back to you soon as I can.
KARI: Wait, Tai, what are you...?
DAIGO: Tai.
TAI: Mr. Nishijima?
What are you doing here?
DAIGO: Get in the truck, and I'll explain.
Come on.
MAN: Is your name Kari?
Uh.
-WOMAN: Every flight canceled. -MAN: Ooh.
This is unacceptable.
MAN: Come on.
For the whole night?
[ Indistinct chatter ]
[ Music playing ]
[ Growling ]
[ Crashing ]
MAN: All units, Code 19 at International Airport.
Repeat. Code 19.
All units respond, over.
WOMAN: Received confirmation that the airport has been
completely shut down,
and, as you can see from our live overhead shot,
there are huge creatures on the runway
- apparently engaging... -Mr. Nishijima, who are you?
[ Music playing ]
[ Growling ]
[ Crashing ]
[ Roaring ]
DAIGO: This is as far as I can take you.
-Good luck. -Thanks.
See you later, whoever you are.
DD1 in position.
Nishijima out.
We're all counting on you, DigiDestined.
Greymon!
[ Growling ]
[ Grunting ]
TAI: [ Grunting ]
[ Music playing ]
GREYMON: [ Grunting ]
[ Crashing ]
Greymon.
MATT: Tai.
[ Music playing ]
Impossible.
I guess you don't know what's going on.
Which is kind of a bummer.
We were hoping you could tell us.
We all just ended up here.
Same thing with you?
Yeah. It's all really confusing.
How are you, Tai?
Are you all right?
Well, now that we're here, let's get to work.
We can finish off Kuwagamon as a team.
It'll be just like old times. Huh?
Hey, wait a sec.
Where's Mimi? She's not here.
And Joe's missing, too.
Huh?
MIMI: Ugh. Why won't Tai answer his blasted phone?
I came all this way just for him, and now he does this?
WOMAN: ...disturbance at International Airport
continues as all flights have been cancelled
amid concerns that the runways are not safe.
There's still no service.
-I can't get through. -Oh.
We've got to get a hold of Mimi.
I can't do anything without her.
[ Growling ]
Hey, Greymon.
[ Panting ]
[ Electronic buzzing ]
Uh-oh. Now there's three of them.
-Agumon. -MATT: I got this, Tai.
-Here we go. Gabumon. -All right.
[ Music playing ]
Gabumon digivolve to...
MAN: [ Singing in Japanese ]
...Garurumon.
Agumon, are you okay?
AGUMON: Tai.
MAN: [ Singing in Japanese ]
Looks like the three of them are splitting up.
Then, we should all do the same.
-Hmm. -Hmm.
That was close. You barely got there in time.
[ Roaring ]
No, you don't.
You're not getting away.
Biyomon.
BIYOMON: On it.
MAN: [ Singing in Japanese ]
Biyomon digivolve to...
[ Music playing ]
MAN: [ Singing in Japanese ]
...Birdramon.
[ Grunting ]
[ Crashing ]
Clobbered him!
It's our turn now, Tentomon!
TENTOMON: Thought you'd never ask.
MAN: [ Singing in Japanese ]
Tentomon digivolve to...
...Kabuterimon.
[ Growling ]
[ Crashing ]
One's getting away.
Let's stop him right here.
Leave it to me, T.K.
And me, too, Kari.
MAN: [ Singing in Japanese ]
Patamon digivolve to...
...Angemon.
[ Grunting ]
[ Explosion ]
[ Crashing ]
Oh, no.
Until Mimi comes, I can't digivolve or help anyone.
That's why I'm going to find Joe.
WOMAN: And officials have confirmed
that all passengers and non-emergency staff
- are now being evacuated... -Is this what I think it is?
WOMAN: ...from International Airport.
As this situation continues to escalate.
Excuse me. You are blocking my view.
WOMAN: Oh, I wouldn't worry about that.
You'll have a close-up view,
and very soon, I promise you.
MIMI: What does that mean?
It just means we are going there right now.
[ Music playing ]
[ Crashing ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Grunting ]
-Ha. -Yes.
MIMI: So the gang's all back together?
But wait.
Are all of them there?
Even Palmon and Gomamon?
I really need to know,
because I have to have enough gifts for everybody.
I can't leave anybody out.
Look at these. Aren't they totally cute?
So your timing is perfect,
'cause I didn't know where to send everything.
[ Sighing ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Music playing ]
Two down.
And one left to go.
[ Crashing ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Grunting ]
Come on. Just get up.
[ Electronic buzzing ]
[ Gasping ]
What was that? Any ideas?
Not a clue.
[ Electronic buzzing ]
Just glad it's over.
We defeated 'em. They won't be coming back.
Yeah. I hope you're right...
...because those Digimon were able to cause
an awful lot of damage during the short amount of time
they were here.
[ Music playing ]
[ Shuddering ]
MATT: I'd like to know more about the humans
who brought us all here.
I'm thinking they must be government men.
They clearly know something.
I asked one of them that, and he wouldn't answer me.
[ Scoffs ]
Well, how can they just drop us in the middle of all this
and not tell us what it's about?
I'm sure our list of questions is only going to grow longer.
Well, one of these guys moonlights as a teacher
because my driver was Mr. Nishijima.
No way.
The guy from our school?
Nishijima's a secret agent?
It's a start, at least.
Maybe we can get some answers from him.
Sure.
But I just get the feeling
this is a whole lot bigger than...
MIMI: Wow! Oh, Palmon's here.
Hi, everyone.
-Mimi! -MIMI: Oh, Palmon!
-You're here. -MIMI: I missed you so much.
-Hey, Mimi. -When did you come back?
Oh, it's so good to see you all.
IZZY: I guess the gang's almost all back together now.
KARI: But if you came back just for this battle,
I'm afraid you missed it, Mimi.
MIMI: I didn't know about any of this until I landed.
It was just a coincidence that I flew back today.
And it was so sweet that you sent a driver
to the airport to pick me up.
Oh, hold on.
I almost forgot.
I've got presents for everybody.
I'm totally into these gummy treats lately,
so I grabbed a whole bunch of them
before I got on the plane.
Aren't they the coolest colors?
Oh, here, Agumon.
You especially look like you could use a treat
-right about now. -Hmm.
[ Chewing ]
Wow. So good.
PALMON: Oh, I wanna try.
-Can I have some? -BIYOMON: Oh, me, too.
MIMI: Yes. Yes.
There's plenty for everybody.
Don't worry. Here you go.
[ Indistinct chatter ]
MIMI: Oh, I brought some for you guys, too.
So you can take them home with you.
That was really kind of you.
Although, now that you mention it, Mimi...
MIMI: How are we getting home?
My driver is waiting right over there.
MATT: So who is she anyway, our driver?
SORA: She's kind of intimidating.
MATT: I'm just glad we all have a ride home.
MIMI: By the way, where are Joe and Gomamon?
T.K.: Good question. We don't know.
TAI: He must have had something pretty important come up.
SORA: Yeah, studying for his entrance exams.
Entrance to what?
SORA: To college, of course.
What else?
What are you thinking about, Izzy?
Nothing. Forget it.
You're falling in love with me, aren't you?
'Cause I came back looking so hot.
What? Stop doing that.
[ Laughing ]
You're so serious.
IZZY: Anyway, Tai's the one who invited you back
so you could come to his soccer match.
MIMI: Yeah, the flight cost a fortune,
-so you owe me. -TAI: What?
Nah, I'm just kidding.
Actually, my dad's work transferred him back here,
so the timing couldn't have been more perfect.
That's right.
I'm here for good.
ALL: Huh? Really?
[ Keyboard clicking ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Knocks on window ]
Huh?
Gomamon?
[ Laughing ]
Yup. I'm back.
[ Gasping ]
[ Chuckling ]
WOMAN: The unidentified creatures
that appeared yesterday
caused massive damage to the city
and the airport.
No serious injuries have been reported.
But the closure of the airport
and the cancelation of all flights in and out
is having a wide-ranging ripple effect
on travel plans throughout the region.
Airlines are trying to resolve the issue.
These are believed to be the same creatures
that have caused so much damage to the city several times
in the past,
only on this occasion,
the appearance of so many of them at one time
meant that the destruction was more extensive than ever.
To get a feeling of how the city was responding
to the incident, we asked several people
for their reactions.
I'm worried that those monsters could come back at any time.
Listen to 'em.
They're acting like there's no difference
between the bad Digimon and the good ones.
Don't these people know
we were trying to stop Kuwagamon?
WOMAN: My daughter is so scared.
I hope that's the last we've seen of them.
WOMAN: An emergency cabinet meeting is underway,
and the government has agreed to cooperate with the police
and self-defense force to handle the situation.
Oh, come on.
If you ask me, it's not like Agumon and Gatomon
are that scary.
BOTH: We're not scary.
They'd like you if they'd just got to know you.
-Yeah. -Yeah.
WOMAN: On a lighter note, the forecast shows
we'll have clear skies for the rest of the day.
TAI: Matt.
You see the news?
-TAI: Yeah. -MATT: Yeah.
WOMAN: My friend's dad was at the airport
when it all happened.
No way. Seriously?
He got hurt. He's in the hospital.
Come on, Tai. Keep moving.
TAI: Hey. Mr. Nishijima?
MAN: He had something to do off-campus.
Anything I can help you with?
[ Sighing ]
Mr. Nishijima's not here today.
SORA: Too bad, we had a ton of questions for him.
WOMAN: See you tomorrow.
Oh, Mimi.
What are you doing here?
I told you. I moved back to the neighborhood,
which means we're all going to the same school again.
And I'm in your class, Izzy.
Great, huh?
[ Sneezing ]
MAN: Ew.
[ Whimpering ]
Excuse me.
Do you know her?
MIMI: Nope. She's a transfer student, too.
But she's older than me, so she's probably in your class.
Really? She's so shy.
[ Bell ringing ]
Well, Izzy? What do you say?
Wanna be a nice guy and show me where our class is?
All right. No problem.
SORA: See you later.
Take it easy.
Heard your soccer match was postponed,
and your band's gig, too, what a drag.
Just 'til things settle down.
-That's all. -Yeah.
We hope.
Hmm.
-I'm Meiko Mochizuki. -Huh?
My family moved here just recently,
and I'm pleased to meet you.
MAN: Thank you, Meiko.
Why don't you take the open seat in the back row,
right next to Tai?
[ Gasping ]
MAN: All right. Now back to work.
Let's review chapter eight.
MAN: So nobody has any idea
why those giant freaks are here?
Or what they want?
MAN: They just showed up and went crazy,
fighting each other and smashing stuff.
Well, let them fight somewhere else.
I hope they wipe each other out.
[ Breathes heavily ]
Hey, calm down.
Calm down?
TAI: It's nothing.
We're cool.
Come on. Do you really think
that getting mad is gonna help anything?
Got a better plan?
SORA: What are you guys doing?
TAI: Just talking.
MATT: What's up, Sora?
SORA: You're both worried about all those
news stories, aren't you?
[ Sighing ]
Let's get together after school.
Oh, there he is.
Over here, Joe.
JOE: Hi. Sorry I'm late.
MIMI: Joe, long time no see!
Look, I brought you a present.
Oh, boy. It's good to see you.
Yeah. You, too, Mimi.
You haven't changed at all.
Thanks for coming by.
I know you're busy and that you should be studying.
No. It's all right.
There's definitely a lot we need to talk about.
Mm-hmm.
IZZY: So, let's review the situation.
I've gathered data on what I see is the six major
recent phenomena.
Okay.
Phenomenon number one, as we all know,
is that the gate to the Digiworld has been closed off
for the last year or so.
I figured that was because our Digivices
have been malfunctioning for some reason.
IZZY: That's phenomenon number two.
Number three, these areas around the waterfront
shopping district have been experiencing
frequency interferences,
with mysterious blackouts occurring right afterward.
Number four, these frequency interferences
are affecting networks that aren't locally connected,
resulting in poor reception for cell phones, radios,
and television broadcasts.
Number five, a distortion in space
caused by unknown forces has created a new link
between us and the Digiworld.
That's how these Digimon are coming into our world.
SORA: Like yesterday's Kuwagamon.
IZZY: Number six, the Digimon coming through this distortion
are different from any we've seen before.
They've been mutated somehow by causes unknown.
Anyway, I think it's safe to assume
that all these phenomena
are a result of this distortion.
Distortion?
They're all interconnected.
I didn't see it at first, but now I'm sure of it.
Each phenomenon is a result of the others.
For example, the frequency interferences
are clearly caused by the distortion
as was proven by what happened yesterday,
and the distortion caused the link
between the Digiworld and ours.
It looks to me like the Digiworld is forcibly
intruding itself into our network.
Hey, Tai. Did you talk to Mr. Nishijima?
TAI: No.
He didn't come to school today.
You guys, did you watch the news?
Did you hear the terrible things they were saying?
Yeah. I heard it.
It was awful.
Like all Digimon are the same.
MATT: Jerks. I'm gonna have my dad file an official complaint.
You know it's just all the media outlets
trying to boost their ratings by sensationalizing everything.
TAI: Still, some of what they said was true.
-Huh? -Huh?
Well, I mean, after all, a lot of the city
and the airport were destroyed when Kuwagamon appeared.
ALL: Hmm.
IZZY: Things are definitely out of control.
T. K.: It's no wonder people are a little upset.
MIMI: Yeah. But it would have been worse
if our Digimon hadn't fought them,
a whole lot worse.
MATT: That's right but nobody knows that.
Our Digimon aren't the problem,
but these news people keep saying they are.
They're pissing me off.
TAI: [ Sighing ]
That's all you got? Come on.
Whose side are you on?
We can't just sit back and do nothing.
You heard what Izzy said.
There's a bunch of really bad things
starting to happen all around us.
We're the only ones who can do something about it.
-TAI: Well, yeah, but... -Yeah, but what?
Have you forgotten everything we've done?
How hard we all fought together
to save the Digital World and our world, too?
Of course I haven't forgotten.
MATT: So what do we do now, then? Nothing?
Okay, then.
[ Sighing ]
Well, Tai?
Calm down. That's enough, Matt.
Yeah. You're right.
Okay. Skip it, Tai.
If that's how you're gonna be,
then, I don't know why we had this meeting in the first place.
IZZY: There has to be a connection...
TAI: Come on, Matt.
IZZY: And I'll bet it's right under my nose.
MATT: [ Sighing ]
-What happened? -We need to figure this out.
-Whatever. -There has to be an answer...
-I'm out of here, too. -...and I'll bet
it's right here at my fingertips.
Don't worry, Sora.
I'll smooth things over with my brother
when I talk to him.
And I'll talk to Tai.
Well, I guess this meeting is adjourned, then.
Just as well. I'm starving, actually.
Does anybody wanna go grab a bite to eat?
JOE: Not me. I gotta study.
Huh?
You know, maybe you could use a break.
I just don't have the time.
I can't even make time for my girlfriend.
ALL: Girlfriend?
Wait a minute.
You have a girlfriend, Joe?
MIMI: I don't believe it. Since when?
A girlfriend? For real?
MIMI: Oh, poor guy. We shouldn't act so shocked.
JOE: What's so weird about that?
I'm nearly out of high school.
Why shouldn't I have a girlfriend?
Don't I have a right to find happiness?
Why doesn't anyone believe me?
We'd better say we believe him, guys.
ALL: We believe you.
JOE: No, you don't. You're just saying that.
Mimi, over here.
-MIMI: Palmon? -Look. Biyomon and Gatomon
are here, too.
ALL: Gatomon?
BOTH: Hi.
[ Music playing ]
You're certainly wearing some funny-looking costumes.
Hmm.
All right.
Sit anywhere you like.
ALL: Okay. Let's dig in.
[ Music playing ]
Oh, boy, it's so yummy.
This is the kind of food I missed the most
while I was away, it's the best.
I agree.
I wish there was someone who could cook like this
in the Digiworld.
Oh, I know, right?
Hot. Okay.
So what were we talking about, anyway?
What to do about Tai and Matt.
What about 'em?
Let them be.
-SORA: But... -You can't keep away from them.
-SORA: Argh. -They did get to be pretty foxy
while I was gone.
Which one do you think's cuter?
[ Coughing ]
[ Music playing ]
SORA: [ Chuckling ]
What's \"foxy\" mean?
I'm not exactly sure.
Oh. Well, anyway, who's your type, Biyomon?
Who do you think is cute?
Well...
GATOMON: Personally, I prefer Lynxy to Foxy.
BIYOMON: Sora would prefer G to E.
Are you still as hungry as I am?
Can we have some more, Sora?
Me, too, please?
Me, three, please?
SORA: Okay, okay. Hang on.
I'll see what I can do.
BIYOMON: Yay.
SORA: Excuse me, ma'am.
[ Music playing ]
MAN: All right. See you tomorrow.
MAN: Okay. Catch you later, man.
Huh?
What are you doing here?
MATT: How about you?
I was gonna go home, but then I just thought
I'd check and see if Mr. Nishijima ever came in.
-Huh? -Huh?
Hmm.
Hey, guys.
That's all one job?
MATT: National Data Processing Bureau Information
and Communication Strategy Section,
Information Management Office,
Management Officer Level Two,
Daigo Nishijima.
Are you even a real teacher?
Yes. But that is my main job.
Lately, a distortion field has formed
between our world and the Digital World,
and Digital Monsters have been using it
instead of the gate to come through.
TAI: Huh.
DAIGO: We've been able to handle them so far,
but now some extremely powerful ones
are starting to appear.
That's why we asked for your help.
We call these new ones infected Digimon.
Infected how?
DAIGO: Certain Digimon are being affected
by some kind of powerful outside force,
which is causing them to go berserk.
Those are the ones we call infected.
Outside force?
DAIGO: Yes, but we don't know what it is yet.
Is there any way these infected Digimon
can ever be returned to normal again?
That's what we're hoping.
There might be a way, but so far
we haven't been able to find one.
MATT: Sounds like there's a lot you don't know yet.
DAIGO: Yeah.
We just wanna send these things back
to where they came from as quickly as possible.
Your group, who exactly are they,
and how did they come by all this information?
I mean, they even know about us.
DAIGO: What happened in Highton View Terrace
and the shopping district
caught a lot of people's attention.
Ever since those incidents,
we've been systematically researching the Digimon,
and we first found out about you
when a person named Gennai contacted us.
So Gennai's working with the government.
Only as a source of information,
and he certainly seems to have
a lot of information on you kids.
TAI: He took care of us a long time ago.
DAIGO: Well, anyway, the next time
any of these infected Digimon appear,
we may need to call on you for help again.
Can we count on you?
Of course. Anytime.
MAN: A number of foreign governments
are requesting that we share our information
regarding the digital monsters.
WOMAN: There's still a lot we don't know.
MAN: Nothing new from the informant known as Gennai?
No, and we're unable to make contact from our end.
MAN: Well, however you get it,
I need more information to pass on.
I understand, sir.
[ Phone vibrating ]
-Yes? -DAIGO: I brought the kids
up to speed.
Right, got it.
What's up, and why are we here?
I thought we were shopping for clothes.
I wanted to beta-test a new computer program
that acts as your own personal shopper.
T.K.: Oh, sure, why not.
IZZY: Until now, my mom's always bought my clothes,
but that was becoming mildly embarrassing.
Now that I'm in high school, I thought it was definitely time
that I start choosing my own clothes.
Yeah, man, break free.
IZZY: But interacting with a living store clerk
always got me nervous.
Oh, I hear 'ya.
IZZY: Interacting with a computer, that's different.
And don't think there's any special reason
why Izzy's suddenly so fashion-conscious,
I mean there's no special reason,
really, hmm.
Ah, it's 'cause of Mimi, isn't it?
[ Laughing ]
You all right there, buddy?
Hittin' the can a little hard.
Anyway, I designed a program that makes it easy
to choose the perfect outfit for any occasion.
I just enter my size and color pallete,
and watch, voila.
I never thought I'd see Izzy all grown up
and buying his own clothes.
Aw, don't cry, Tentomon.
It's okay.
AGUMON: Tai?
Is something bothering you?
What is it, Tai?
[ Playing harmonica ]
Hmm, what's wrong, Matt?
What is it?
It's about Tai.
He's changed.
I just wonder if everyone's gonna start changing.
But you're friends.
TAI: Matt hasn't changed a bit.
AGUMON: Huh?
TAI: I can understand why he'd get angry.
Maybe he's right and I'm wrong.
What do you think?
AGUMON: I think you'll figure it out.
[ Music playing ]
TAI: I'm scared.
AGUMON: Huh?
TAI: We do so much damage without even realizing it.
We destroy things,
and not just buildings.
It might be people one day.
I guess it's a little late to start worrying
about that kind of stuff, huh?
AGUMON: Oh, Tai.
[ Music playing ]
KARI: I didn't know you were going to be
-bringing Agumon with you. -TAI: Of course.
KARI: Well, now, I wish Gatomon and Patamon
had come with us.
Matt couldn't come. Something came up.
Yeah. And Joe's not going to be able to make it, either.
So, this is yours now, Izzy?
IZZY: Yup. Not bad, huh?
TAI: Not bad at all.
I'll get that.
Yes. Who is it?
MIMI: It's me, Mimi.
Whoa. I love it.
What is this place, anyway?
It's Izzy's office. Can you believe it?
No way. Seriously?
Yeah. We've never seen it before, either.
Yeah. I'm helping out a friend who's starting a new company.
I'm impressed.
Really, Izzy?
TAI: Anyway, that's about everything
Mr. Nishijima told us.
IZZY: Infected Digimon, huh?
And these things could come back at any time?
That's pretty annoying.
I'm sure glad you and the other Digimon
have come to help us, Biyomon.
Izzy, don't you think it's time to show everyone
what you've come up with?
Yeah. You're right. Let's do it.
TENTOMON: Okay. You two, come with me.
One, two, three,
in you go.
-Agumon. -Biyomon.
No need to worry.
They're right there.
Izzy: Check it out. I thought our Digimon
should have a place they can escape to
in an emergency,
so I created a secure virtual cyberspace
on my server here.
[ Phone ringing ]
SORA: Biyomon just texted me.
How do I work this thing again?
There, look. You got a text, too, from Agumon.
You can communicate by texting
or by talking directly through the monitors.
Wow. That's genius.
SORA: But they can come back out, right?
BIYOMON: See?
Easy-peasy.
SORA: That's a relief.
Can we summon them with our cell phone?
No, they don't have enough processing speed,
but they can easily come in and out
of the virtual cyberspace
through a large monitor connected to a network,
as long as I specify which one.
T.K.: So, then, we can summon them any time?
IZZY: Precisely. They'll either be here in this office
or in the secure virtual cyberspace.
SORA: Oh, my gosh. Look at the time!
KARI: Good thing we don't have to take the stairs.
T.K.: So, I guess nothing's changed between
you and Tai since you didn't show up at Izzy's today.
When are you guys gonna call a truce and work things out?
Pouting about it's not helping.
Hey, I'm not pouting.
T.K.: If you say so. Anyway,
we're all planning to meet up again Saturday.
You better come this time. Later.
The last thing we need to be doing right now
is fighting each other.
What if Kuwagamon comes back?
We've got to pull together.
KARI: Izzy, were you up all night?
You look like a zombie.
SORA: A zombie who hasn't eaten in a while.
IZZY: I'm okay. I slept a little bit.
What I was working on couldn't wait.
And I finally finished these.
-Try 'em, Tai. -TAI: Oh, yeah.
If my calculations are correct,
the goggles should let you see
-the wavelength distortions. -Wow.
TAI: These are even better than my old goggles.
Tai, we're going to hang out in the digital room
that Izzy made for us.
If you need us, just call, okay?
Can they just go through the screen on your laptop?
Yes, but as long as we're outside here,
let's try a little test of the system.
That ATM should be connected to the web.
Just call, and we'll come running.
TAI: Thanks, Agumon.
[ Electronic buzzing ]
Well, that worked.
SORA: What should we do now, Izzy?
Let's test the goggles.
My research shows that the wavelength distortions
are easiest to see in places
where there's a lot of data.
So, Tai should be able to see the dataflow
when he puts the goggles on.
The different colored streams
represent different types of data
and how strong they are.
When I connect the goggles to my server like this,
you should see even more of them.
TAI: Whoa. You're right, Izzy.
Now there's more streams, and the colors got brighter.
The red streams are the ones that match up
the closest with the big distortions.
And those are the ones we think
the infected Digimon are coming through,
so tracking the red streams
may tell us when they're coming.
Yeah. That would help.
IZZY: This open area should be a good place
to test that theory.
Let's see if Tai spots any distortions
that look like they might be dangerous.
SORA: Hey, isn't that the new girl?
She looks like she might be lost or something.
Meiko,
are you lost?
MIMI: Maybe we can help you.
Well, in fact, you're right.
I was looking for something,
but I ended up just getting lost myself.
Oh, believe me, I can relate.
Huh? Really?
Maybe we can help each other,
'cause it just so happens
we're looking for something ourselves.
Yeah. Join us.
-MEIKO: Uh. -Come on, guys.
Try to keep up.
This is kind of a big place.
What exactly are you looking for?
Well, it's, uh...
like a cat, sort of.
Hmm? Sort of?
Well, either it is a cat or it isn't a cat, right?
What other options are there?
MEIKO: Well, uh...
T.K.: Okay. We'll let the girls deal with the imaginary cat.
Hey, Tai, what do the goggles show here?
TAI: Hmm, not much, and no red streams at all.
It looks pretty safe to me.
SORA: Hey, have you ever been in this store over here?
They have really cute stuff.
IZZY: Why are we scanning for data streams in here, Tai?
We're not.
I was just super hungry.
MAN: Most of you did well on the test,
but those few with scores below 80
are to report here Saturday morning
to take the exam again.
Oh.
[ Sighing ]
[ Whooshing ]
[ Thunder rumbling ]
MEIKO: I really appreciate your help,
but I'm gonna keep looking for my... cat on my own.
-Thanks. -SORA: You sure?
It's no trouble at all.
MEIKO: Yes, I'm sure, but thanks again.
SORA: Well, okay. Good luck.
TAI: Hey, Izzy. I was wondering about something.
-IZZY: What is it? -The goggles worked great
but I can only see streams that are at close range.
I bet I could see more if we were up on some high ground.
But there aren't any big hills here.
I know a way we can get way up in the air.
IZZY: The Ferris wheel.
Genius, Kari.
T.K.: Look who the imaginary cat dragged in.
Hey, come on.
Glad you came.
Why wouldn't I come?
Ah, why can't you ever just lighten up?
Stay behind, if you want, but I'm going on the ride.
IZZY: He doesn't seem happy to be here.
MATT: Why are we doing this, anyway?
Tai can explain it. You'll have plenty of time.
-MATT: Hey. -TAI: Hey.
Wait a minute. Stop.
Come on.
[ Laughing ]
Got 'em! That worked out perfectly.
They're finally alone.
Now, maybe they can end that stupid argument.
Huh? I didn't know they were arguing.
SORA: Well, more like not arguing.
And since they've been acting like bratty kids,
I decided to give them a time-out.
What do you think, Kari?
Is this gonna work?
Well, at least, they'll talk.
-MATT: Listen. -Mmm.
Sorry about the other day.
I didn't mean to get so ticked off,
but the truth is you need to get your act together,
because it's only a matter of time
before more infected Digimon show up.
What's going on in your head?
This isn't like you.
The old you would have taken action.
TAI: I don't know what to do.
It's not like when we were kids.
[ Music playing ]
These days, it feels like I see more,
but I understand less.
Is fighting the answer?
It might seem right at the time...
but maybe it's not.
I still believe we're the only ones
who can fix this.
I'm just worried.
What if we make it worse?
[ Matt scoffing ]
Huh?
Oh, spare me.
-Look. -What?
MATT: Quit trying to run away from it.
TAI: I'm not.
GABUMON: I wish I could hear what they're talking about.
Probably swapping jokes.
MATT: Nice goggles.
Any reason you decided to bring 'em along?
Oh, yeah. I almost forgot.
Whoa, a big distortion.
Tons of red streams.
[ Thunder rolling ]
MATT: Hey, where are we going?
WOMAN: Attention, all waterfront visitors,
a severe weather front is forming over the harbor,
and a weather emergency situation has been declared.
All visitors are advised to evacuate
the waterfront immediately
and make your way inland and to shelter.
I repeat, this is a mandatory evacuation order
for the entire waterfront area.
Please make your way in a safe, orderly manner
to the nearest shelter.
WOMAN: We'd better get going.
TAI: I've got a feeling something big is coming.
Big and bad.
Where are the DigiDestined?
MAN: I don't know.
I haven't been able to reach any of them yet.
WOMAN: Let's get out of here.
MEIKO: Meicoomon!
Meicoomon, where are you?
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Crashing ]
[ Electrical buzzing ]
BOY: Hurry, let's get out of here.
Oh, no, what's that?
Never seen anything like it.
Found it, it's called Alphamon.
Any weaknesses?
Unfortunately, there's no data on it,
only the name and the image.
How do we stop it?
We need help.
Summon our Digimon, Izzy.
That's a good idea.
It's here.
The one.
Meicoomon!
Meicoomon, where are you?
[ Gasping ]
MEICOOMON: Meiko.
Meicoomon!
Oh, I'm so glad I found you.
I'm glad, too, but you're safe now.
[ Sneezing ]
[ Electronic whine ]
[ Explosion ]
[ Screaming ]
Why her?
This is no time for holding back.
I got you.
Hang on.
[ Electronic whine, explosion ]
[ Grunting ]
-Are you okay? -Mm-hmm.
GABUMON: Matt.
MATT: Well, what do you know!
Gabumon.
Everything is gonna be all right.
Let's do this, Gabumon.
[ Roaring ]
[ Crashing, electronic whine ]
[ Crashing ]
-Birdramon. -Kabuterimon.
[ Music playing ]
[ Grunting ]
Tai!
We're gonna need Omnimon!
[ Crashing ]
Palmon, get in there.
You got it.
[ Music playing ]
Palmon digivolve to...
Togemon.
-Our turn. -Oh, yeah.
How about a little needle spray?
[ Electronic whine ]
Uh, Tai?
TAI: What am I supposed to do?
MEIKO: I will never give you Meicoomon.
Huh?
MEIKO: Never, forget it.
[ Gasping ]
TAI: I've got to do something.
[ Music playing ]
[ Electronic whine ]
[ Yelling ]
AGUMON: Tai.
You're really just gonna sit there?
We didn't start this fight,
but we are the only ones with the power to end it.
If you don't act, everything is going to be destroyed,
not just buildings, but people.
Only we can stop this.
[ Music playing ]
Hmm.
All right. Agumon.
Yup, ready to rock Tai.
Yeah.
Where's Garurumon?
Metal Greymon.
[ Explosions ]
Metal Garurumon.
[ Ice shattering ]
War Greymon.
[ Electronic buzzing ]
Omnimon.
[ Gasping ]
Prodigious.
[ Electronic whine ]
[ Swords clashing ]
[ Crashing ]
[ Gasping ]
Hmm.
[ Electronic whine ]
[ Explosion ]
Yeah!
Uh-oh.
[ Grunting ]
[ Electronic buzzing ]
[ Electronic whine ]
[ Explosion ]
[ Gasping ]
Huh?
ALL: [ Gasp ]
[ Scoffing ]
Too bad it got away.
Guys.
Are you all right?
Huh?
IZZY: I'll take that as a yes.
[ Sighing ]
ALL: Huh?
KARI: Oh, is that who you were searching for?
Yes, I found her.
So, this is May? I heard you calling her.
I call her May, but her name is Meicoomon.
IZZY: Meicoomon, huh?
Fascinating.
You see, I have a Digimon partner, too.
ALL: [ Gasp ]
That means you're also a DigiDestined.
Well, yeah. I guess I am.
[ Laughing ]
So cool.
I'm sorry...
I should've told you.
TAI: So our team just got bigger.
Welcome aboard.
Thank you. We're so lucky we met all of you.
What do you say to our new friends, Meicoomon?
Done-done.
Huh? Say what?
[ Gasping ]
That's \"thank you\" in Meicoomon speak.
ALL: [ Laugh ]
[ Music playing ]
[ Singing in Japanese ]
WOMAN: In breaking news, another unidentified creature
has caused massive destruction.
Multi--
Have you made up your mind yet?
Fine, then, I'm as tired of talking
about this stuff as you are.
Thanks for sticking around, really appreciate it.