(static crackling)
(wind rustling)
- Where am I?
Where is everyone?
(gun bangs)
(guns banging)
(soft twinkling music)
- Hey, Remy.
Stick close to us or we'll lose you.
- Where are we?
- Who knows?
- [Remy] Where are we going?
- Can't say.
It's nothing new for us.
(crow squawks)
(uplifting music)
(soft music)
- Where am I?
(fly buzzing)
Where...
Oh, yeah.
That hotel in the city we found.
I got a single.
Now it's coming back.
(water rushing)
(Remy yelps)
Huh?
What?
No water again?
This is certainly no planet for girls.
(Remy yawns)
(bell tolling)
(ominous music)
Wonder if the others are up yet.
(helicopter blades whirring)
- [Reporter] And the criminals
who robbed the City 13 branch
of the Three Mark Bank at 2:20
continue their flight from justice
in three air cars containing the hostages
and 3.4 billion in gold bullion.
(sirens wailing)
All city expressways have been locked off
with civilian traffic far from access.
Because of this,
city traffic is backed
up for five kilometers
with no relief in sight.
The criminals are believed
to be carrying heavy weaponry
leaving the patrol cars in a
cautious pursuit behind them.
Oh!
Oh dear! (screams)
(static crackling)
(Remy sighs)
(horns honking)
- [Remy] Had to happen today, didn't it?
What do I do?
I'll never make it at this rate.
And the expressways are practically empty.
That's right.
I don't have much time left.
To hell with this.
Let's go.
(car thuds)
Sorry.
(police radio chatters)
- Huh?
- Stop! Stop!
Hey, stop!
God!
- What's that?
- It looks like a freeway ticket.
At least he's not trying
to sneak a free ride.
(police officer groans)
- What the hell's the matter with you?
After him!
- [Officer] License plate
reads S-E-E-Y-O-U-A-G-A-I-N.
Got the owner.
Remy Shimada.
A woman!
- [Officer 2] Remy Shimada.
Traveled space as a member
of the GoShogun Team.
Winner of the Galaxy Award for Valor.
Refused acceptance.
(sirens wailing)
- [Officer] Great technique.
You think she'd give me her autograph?
- [Officer 2] Kinda doubt it.
- [Officer] Doesn't even look like
she likes getting her picture taken.
- [Officer 2] This photo's pretty old.
- [Officer] A woman of mystery.
- [Officer 2] You think so?
She turned down the
Galaxy Award 40 years ago.
- [Officer] 40 years?
You mean...
- [Officer 2] The Remy
Shimada driving that car
is over 70 years old.
(upbeat music)
- Out of the way.
(horn honks)
Come on!
(gun banging rapidly)
Give me a break, will you?
I'm just in a hurry.
I don't have any beef with you guys.
(groans) I was gonna get a
good price for this thing!
Okay, if that's the way you want it.
(upbeat music continues)
(gun banging rapidly)
(explosion booms)
(sirens wailing)
One down.
And the next one.
(glass shatters)
(tires squealing)
- [Officer] We got the perps and recovered
all the hostages too.
- [Officer 2] Damn! What a woman!
- Swell.
Better put out that fire on my ass.
I guess I'm not gonna make it.
(Remy gasps)
(tires squealing)
Look out!
(somber music)
Mamma?
Where is this place?
Where am I?
Mamma?
(man grunts)
- Who's the kid?
- [Mother] Remy, didn't I
tell you not to come here?
- But, uh...
But...
(man grunts)
- This little one's yours, huh?
Mm.
She's gonna be a real
looker when she grows up.
- Get away from her!
She'll never have to sell herself!
- What the hell are you doing?
(mother gasps)
(man gasps)
- Your time's up.
Pay and get out and
leave my daughter alone!
- I ain't coming back.
(door slams)
(Remy sobs)
- [Mother] Remy, Mamma
has more work to do.
Buy something nice for yourself
and wait for me at home.
(Remy sniffling)
- That was the first and last time
Mother ever gave me pocket money.
One chocolate crepe and 10
sweet broiled chestnuts later,
it was gone.
I don't even remember how they tasted.
And there was Mother's
death not long after that.
These are the only memories
I have left of her.
(bell dings)
(soft music)
- [Killy] We meet again, Shingo.
- [Shingo] Yeah. God, Killy, 40 years.
- I'd forgotten just how
much time had passed.
You want one?
- No smoking in the museum.
So how long have you been smoking, anyway?
- [Killy] The day we stopped fighting
was the day there stopped
being any point to not smoking.
Jesus.
You mean you and she never
got it together in 40 years?
- [Shingo] Look who's talking,
you second-rate Casanova.
There was never anything between
Remy and me, to my regret.
- [Killy] We never had anything either.
What a couple of jerks we are,
wasting poor Remy like that.
The only ones left are
his royal Bundle-ness
and the other two.
- [Shingo] Looks like those
three won't be coming today.
- But Remy.
What would get her to
call us out here now?
- I don't know.
Anyway, she's late.
(monitor beeping)
(machine whooshing)
- [Doctor] She has no relatives?
- [Officer] Yeah, and
her house was locked up
like she was a hermit or something.
- What about her hospital expenses?
- No savings account at all.
- But she was the winner
of the Galaxy Award.
Can't the government cover it?
- Well, she never actually accepted
and she hasn't had anything to
do with the government since.
- What about health insurance coverage?
- [Officer] Defaulted on the premiums.
- Huh, so who is going
to pay for the treatment
we've already given her up till now?
- At 6:30 will be dinner
with the president
of the All World Banking Union.
You'll be discussing
financing for the coming year.
At 7:30 will be a party hosted
by the Fishery, Agriculture,
and Industrial Unions.
They request you make a 20 minute speech.
(phone ringing)
President's office.
Sir, phone call for you.
- [Kernagul] From who?
- A hospital apparently.
- Hospital?
Yeah?
What is it?
What?
Hospital costs?
We've got a company health plan.
Just...
What do you mean she isn't even on it?
Why the devil should I pay for someone
who isn't even in my company?
This isn't a charity I'm running.
Huh? Galaxy Award?
The woman who turned it down.
Go and cancel everything
that's on my schedule tonight.
- But there's a round table meeting
with the president after the party.
- I don't care!
(secretary gasps)
- Yes, sir.
- Remy's been injured.
(soft music)
- [Killy] Closing time.
End of show.
Curtain falls.
- [Shingo] You'd drop the curtain
before the heroin's entrance?
- [Woman] Mr. Shingo Hojo
and Mr. Killy Gagley?
- [Shingo] Yes?
- [Woman] I have a message for you
from the president of Kernagul Fried.
Miss Remy Shimada cannot join you today.
- Huh?
(monitor beeping)
(machine whooshing)
- In here.
- So, how is she?
(Kernagul grunts)
- The examination revealed a problem
in addition to the wounds
she received in the accident.
Progressive Leuko-Isolation Syndrome.
- Leuko-Isolation Syndrome.
- If we'd known about it earlier
we could've done something to correct it.
Look here.
It spread throughout her body.
As it is, she has a 5%
chance for recovery.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Well, taking into account the accident,
I'd give her two days.
(all gasp)
- Huh? What?
Two days?
You just said she had a 5% chance.
- That's true, if we
got hold of a specialist
at the City University Hospital.
But relations between the Central Hospital
and the University
Hospital aren't that great
and her injuries are very serious.
If we moved her, she'd
die within the hour.
(doctor yelps)
- Then I suggest you call the guy
at the University Hospital
right now, doctor.
- Hey, stop it. Don't kill him.
He's the only hope for treatment.
(doctor grunts)
(doctor coughs)
- There's just too much red tape.
It'd be different if we
had an official order
from the Surgeon General's office.
- Surgeon General?
(chuckles) The surgeon General?
(Kernagul laughs)
- What's with you?
- Our Surgeon General's
a man that the big wigs
on the Federation Council
know pretty damn well.
- You wouldn't mean...
- Oh yeah!
Mr. Caw-Caw Crow, the joker who accepted
the Galaxy Award with us.
- So where is he now?
(owl hoots)
(car thuds)
(Cuttnal grunts)
- Oh, Christ.
Why does my job have me bouncing around
these goddamned mountains?
(Cuttnal grunts)
Oh, Christ.
(crow squawks)
(peaceful music)
- Sun and moon are like travelers
moving for 100 generations to and fro.
Time passes unconcerned,
the starlight unchanging,
making the darkness to night
all the more beautiful.
The taste of Shadojima style somen noodles
is pleasing to my palate.
Yet I find the slim but firm Miwa style
much more suitable,
with Welsh onions the
only seasoning necessary.
- Bundle.
(Cuttnal sighs)
Somen isn't much of a meal by itself.
You should add some
fried eggs or ham to it,
just like I taught you.
- At least I'm not the one
eating cold Chinese food.
- Ah, don't be like that.
We're both getting old.
And that means we have to
eat well and cooperate.
Here, my friend, just sign this.
- [Bundle] And what is this?
- Only the title to this land.
Huh?
- I shan't help a corrupt politician
evict me from my own land.
- What the?
Don't be like that.
Despite what you think of me,
I am the Surgeon General.
I want to turn this into
a public health resort.
It has to be developed.
Be a pal.
What?
- This plot of nature is
never to be developed.
Now leave this place
while you can.
(Cuttnal screams)
- All right, all right,
all right, all right!
- [Bundle] That's better.
- Jesus Christ, if he
wasn't such an old friend,
I'd bulldoze this shack in a second.
You know I would.
- You'd what?
- Nothing! Nothing!
(laughs) You got good
ears for a man your age.
Ah hell, I'm the one
that's going deaf lately.
(machine ringing)
Huh?
It's for me.
Hello?
Well I'm kinda in the middle
of something right now.
Remy Shimada?
Yeah, I know her.
What, what? Uh-huh, yeah.
She's in critical?
You need my authorization?
Oh, there's no way I'll make it
down these mountains in two days.
- Cuttnal.
- Huh?
(peaceful music)
- Leave this to me.
The city's only 50 minutes
away at supersonic.
Sword and saber alone are
not enough in today's world.
This too is a requirement of the Samurai.
(ship whooshes)
(metal sparking)
- Even with the rain, it isn't any cooler.
Probably why the guys haven't
come out of their rooms.
(locket clicks)
A locket with no one inside.
(knocking on door)
Everyone gets tired of
being alone eventually.
(locket clicks)
Shingo, Killy, Kernagul, Cuttnal?
Or is it you, Bundle?
(soft twinkling music)
Yes?
- [Messenger] Here. This is for you.
- Why, thank you.
Wait!
Who sent this?
(soft music)
In two days you will be dead.
That is your destiny.
How you die is shown within.
In two days you will be dead.
How you die will be...
- [Cuttnal] Get that specialist
at University Hospital now
and tell him it's an order
from the Surgeon General.
(monitor beeping)
(machine whooshing)
- [Killy] Thanks,
Cuttnal. You've saved her.
- Well...
I don't think she'll be
able to pull through.
Remy's condition is progressively
getting worse as we speak,
even with the operation.
I only give her 1% chance of survival.
- 1%? Jesus.
- 1%?
- No.
Remy's spirit defies all the odds.
Her will to live itself
has always been a thing of
beauty, even now surely.
- (chuckles) What's wrong, Remy?
Don't you want it?
Just take off your dress.
- Yeah, come on.
We'll buy it from you.
(bullies laughing)
Come on.
Just do it!
(bullies laughing)
(bullies gasp)
(upbeat music)
(fist thudding)
(bullies crying)
- Thanks, friends.
I'll just take this for my cleaning bill.
See ya!
- [Bully] Mommy!
(ominous music)
(Remy panting)
(Remy yelps)
(Remy yelping)
(Remy panting)
(Remy screams)
(ominous music continues)
- [Messenger] This will
be you in two days time.
You will die in the most shameful of ways,
ripped apart, body and soul, by strangers.
A baptism of blood awaits you.
- Well, thanks for the warning.
(water rushing)
What's that?
Did I forget to turn it off?
(Remy yelps)
(tense music)
Real funny.
(upbeat music)
I don't mean to scare you
but I need to know something.
What are the guest room
water pipes connected to?
- The water tank on the roof.
- [Remy] Thanks.
- Remy, don't shoot!
There's no one up here.
- Except us, that is.
Nothing but water in there.
- Blood! Blood!
- I hate having blood
running all over the place.
Huh?
Oh, it's just you guys.
- [Killy] There isn't a
drop of blood up here.
- So you guys saw it too?
- Every one of us got
those bloody love letters.
It seems someone apparently
wants us all dead.
- A baptism of blood.
I'd prefer one of fine wine, thank you.
Perhaps a bordeaux.
(thunder crashes)
- Those who receive the
baptism will surely die.
You, in two days.
No one can escape their destiny.
It is written.
(pleasant music)
(Killy grunts)
(water dripping)
- [Bully] That's her.
She's the one who stole my money.
- [Bully's Mother] You
little tramp. How dare yoU!
I'm taking you to the police.
(Bully's mother yells)
(gentle music)
(Remy screams)
- Where is this?
Where am I?
(Remy whimpering)
(thunder crashes)
- [Officer] I understand your situation.
But it wouldn't do to raise a fuss
over this sort of thing.
- [Killy] This sorta thing?
- Quickly vanishing baptisms
of blood and letters of fate
are quite common things in this city.
- Like hell it's common.
You don't see that much blood
in boxing or pro wrestling.
- When death draws near,
everyone here receives a letter of fate
and the baptism of blood.
They then pray to God
and prepare their souls.
- Correct.
No man may change the fate God grants him.
Even to strangers like yourselves.
- Poppycock!
My medicines have saved
lots of people's lives.
I've changed people's fates!
(thunder crashes)
(Shingo gasps)
- Look out!
(chandelier crashes)
(Cuttnal groaning)
- You see that? He saved me.
Stuff that in your letters of fate
and smoke it, you old biddy.
- Your letter did not
decree your death this day.
Your destiny remains unchanged.
- Do not attempt to leave this hotel.
Our people do not take kindly
to those who defy fate.
(bell tolling)
- Sunset prayer is called.
Come. We must pray to God.
(ominous music)
- So now what?
- Wait, I'm pretty sure
he told us not to leave.
- Making that option
all the more appealing.
I'll pack.
- I was starting to go all out stir crazy
in that room anyway.
- Let's chase the blues away.
- I'm with you. Let's go.
(Remy giggles)
(pool balls rattling)
- [Cuttnal] Like the old woman said,
I'm supposed to die in four days.
- [Kernagul] Five days for me.
- [Killy] Three for me.
- Four.
I see no point in keeping a tally.
- Hmm.
Well, guys, looks like
I'll be the first to go.
That's good.
I wouldn't wanna be around
to see any of you die anyway.
- We won't let that happen, Remy.
- I've never had anything in my life.
Damned if I go out that way.
And neither will Remy if I can help it.
- I say we just blow this joint, right?
- That's with Remy, of course.
- Thanks, guys.
No, really. Thanks.
Oh, hell. Lighten up.
Let's make the best of this.
Bottoms up.
- [All] Cheers!
(glasses clink)
(smooth music)
- It's still too soon to
harvest this lovely rose.
- Huh?
- No mercy for those who
defy the God of fate.
- What do you say, guys?
You're a little early, aren't ya?
- Your fate will not change.
You will not die, no matter
how badly we beat you.
- I gotcha.
Sorta like a divine carte blanche.
- Well, we can cut loose without worrying.
- Extreme as always.
(smooth music continues)
- The only ones fated to
get beaten are you guys.
(all grunting)
(fists thudding)
- I haven't danced in ages.
(Remy chuckles)
Let's make a hot date hotter.
(Kernagul grunting)
- Why all the violence? (chuckles)
Are you all right?
Have some medicine, huh?
Here.
(laughs) Just my sleeping aids.
(all grunting)
(glass shattering)
- Pardon me.
Hope I didn't disturb your playing.
- Not at all, my dear.
A forte seemed quite
appropriate at that point.
- Your piano playing just makes me wanna
kick up my heels and dance.
- Hold on.
We are here for your protection.
(gun bangs)
Clear out, rioters.
(guns banging rapidly)
- This is insane!
You're cops and you act like that?
What's the matter with you?
- [Officer] We protect the
citizenry from rioters.
- [Killy] And I suppose
that this was their fate?
- Correct.
As you have your own fates to meet.
Until then, stay in your hotel
for the sake of civil
order, at the very least.
- Don't you worry one bit.
We're leaving your happy little city.
- There is no outside to this place.
You're now one of us.
No one can escape this city.
- Just as no one can escape
his destiny, Officer?
- Just as you say.
(sirens wailing)
- The whole city's our enemy.
- Somebody's pulling their
strings in the background.
- [Killy] That thing the worship?
- [Shingo] Probably.
- Do we take it down?
- There is no beauty in a hopeless battle.
- Then we just run like hell?
- Running's nothing new to me.
(Remy giggles)
(ominous music)
(Remy sighs)
(future Remy screams)
(Remy gasps)
(creature growls)
- This will be you in two days time.
- Disgusting!
(Remy groaning)
(creature growling)
(gun bangs)
- You won't be able to
kill it with bullets.
(gun banging)
I said you couldn't.
(blood squelching)
(bones crunching)
Now look at how you're going to die.
- Fine, I'll look.
It's your foolishness I see.
I don't know who you think you are,
but you won't win!
(fabric rips)
(future Remy groaning)
- Why don't you just give in?
You can't win.
Be patient. Just two more days.
(Remy moaning)
(soft music)
(basket rustling)
(cat meows)
(Remy giggles)
(Remy yells)
(Remy groaning)
(gun bangs)
- [Killy] Remy! Use the knife!
(Remy panting)
- Thank you, Killy.
- By the looks of things,
you're at least a century or
two ahead of these jokers.
- But why are you here?
- Well, you kinda tipped us off
when you jumped out your window.
You always had to have
your own way and go solo.
We figured it looked like
you could use our help.
Listen, Remy, please let us
protect you just for once
and no arguments.
- Look, I guess I just
like to pull my own weight.
- If you survive, then
maybe Mr Fate over there
won't look so tough.
And maybe I'll still
be alive in three days.
- [Remy] Killy.
- Come on. We're all together on this.
Looks like the party's coming our way.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hang on.
This gun's way too big for rapid fire.
If you shoot too much,
you'll hurt your hand.
- Yeah, I know.
But I'm used to it, really.
- Okay, get going.
I'll take care of everything here.
No, no, no.
I don't wanna hear another word.
Remember, I die in three days.
I'll catch you later.
- Mm-hmm. See ya.
- Come on.
(ominous music)
(dramatic music)
(Remy grunting)
(gun banging)
- Get away!
(tense music)
(gun bangs)
- Remy, now's your chance.
Get up here!
(gun banging)
- Shingo!
- You can thank me later.
(explosion booms)
These things aren't human.
We can't use normal tactics.
- [Remy] Where do they keep coming from?
- How long do you figure it'll
take them to get up here?
- As much as I'd like
them to take their time,
I'd say about a minute.
- It's enough.
(tense music continues)
- Over here, boys.
Good job on your graveyard shift.
Bye-bye!
(explosion booms)
Tough luck, guys.
(both grunting)
(both yelp)
They're persistent.
- Remy, run for it.
I can handle this by myself.
- No way. I'll stay and help.
- Don't be stupid and
make this all for nothing.
- But...
- I'm team leader and
that's a direct order.
Seems old habits are hard to break.
Go.
- Mm-hmm.
Shingo, thanks.
- This is all that I seem
to be good for anyway.
(gun banging)
(explosion booms)
- Better reload.
(Remy winces)
Did I overdo it with the gun?
I can't move my fingers.
(tense music)
On bicycles now?
I think I'm beginning to
lose this little footrace.
Well, considering I'm facing
a pretty nasty death anyway.
(gun bangs)
(Remy winces)
- Remy, get on.
Anymore fighting is quite pointless.
Don't waste your ammunition on them.
- Bundie, cool bike.
Where'd you get it?
- I borrowed it from the police.
My natural abilities at work.
- [Remy] Living up to your name, I see.
- It isn't stolen.
Merely rented without
the benefit of paperwork.
- [Remy] Mm.
- We have to get out of this city.
The sooner the better off we'll be.
- What about the other guys?
- We still have some things to do.
(energetic music)
The exit!
- And a big goddamn welcome wagon.
But they aren't attacking.
- Let's do it!
(audio warbles)
(Remy gasps)
- But that's impossible.
(guns clicking)
- You cannot leave this city.
It'll be the same every time you try.
Your only escape is when the god of fate
decrees that you sleep in that graveyard.
(ominous music)
(monitor beeping)
- [Doctor] You'd better
make the arrangements.
- [Nurse] Yes, Doctor.
- And keep it from that entourage of hers.
- Understood.
(heartbeat pounding)
- No one's coming.
No one's here.
- [Mysterious Voice] Right.
No one's coming.
No one's here.
- It's so quiet.
Yeah, Mamma's buried here too.
- [Mysterious Voice] Yes,
Mamma and I will be together.
- So I guess I'm gonna die.
- [Mysterious Voice] You will.
That was decided the day you were born.
- So, this is it.
- [Mysterious Voice] Yes.
There's no escape from this darkness.
It was decided from the beginning.
(soft music)
(bell tolling)
- So, tomorrow's the day.
At least I got water
today, thank goodness.
(Remy winces)
- It'll be tomorrow.
You're going to die.
Are you ignoring me?
- No, you wouldn't let me even if I tried.
But it's time for little
girls to be in bed.
Just take your precious
little pet and go home now.
- You will die in agony.
- Nighty-night, little girl.
(creature growling)
(soft twinkling music)
Seven rounds, huh?
I doubt that I'll even mange
to get six of them off.
An empty locket.
(uplifting music)
I would really hate to see it go to waste.
(soft music)
- [Shingo] In the end,
it's always this one.
- And in the end, I have nothing.
Nothing at all, no matter
how I looked at it.
The Autobiography of Killy
Gagley: The Bronx Wolf.
Volume one, 10th revised edition.
The end.
(Killy sighs)
Ah, hell.
There's no way it'll get
past one volume anyway.
- Nothing more can be said.
The glitter of this blade,
polished to perfection,
is a beauty which never fades.
People are no different.
(welding rod whooshing)
- You know, I was pretty
damn good with my hands
when I was a little kid.
Used to build plastic model kits
I'd steal from stores.
- My family was so elite
that I didn't have that many friends.
I built lots of super alloy model kits.
Purchased, of course, with my
American Express gold card.
(both sighing)
I miss those days, just being a kid.
- I really miss our common interest.
- Gloomy.
Damn gloomy.
(tools clattering)
- [Both] Don't squawk!
(crow squawks quietly)
(bell tolling)
(bright music)
(Remy chuckles)
(singing in foreign language)
- Hey there!
You guys need a lift?
- We're giving our project a test run.
Free rides to the enemy cathedral.
(bell chimes)
- Okay, all aboard!
(metal sparking)
Full speed ahead.
- My body's so cold.
So, so cold.
- [Mysterious Voice] Yes,
your sleep has come this far.
- It's not right, just dying like this.
It's not right.
- [Mysterious Voice]
There's nothing you can do.
Just give up.
This is all you could've
expected from your life.
- Yeah, I guess you're right.
- [Mysterious Voice]
Adieu, farewell, Remy.
- Adieu, whoever you are.
- [Mysterious Voice 2] Don't
give her that adieu stuff.
- [Mysterious Voice 3] Yeah, he's right.
- Who's there?
- [Mysterious Voice 3] Who?
Well, you haven't met us yet
but there's a chance you will.
You're one of us!
- One of you?
I don't have any friends.
- [Mysterious Voice 4] Not friends.
We're all alone like you.
So you're one of us.
- You're all alone too?
- [Mysterious Voice 5]
I've never had anything
since I was born.
No parents, no brothers or sisters,
or even a house with lights in it.
- [Mysterious Voice 3] My
parents died when I was little.
Right now I'm in military school
studying how to be a spy,
so I don't have any friends.
We all live in different places,
all of us alone.
- [Mysterious Voice 4] But we
think we might meet someday.
- [Mysterious Voice 5]
Of course, we don't know
for sure if we will.
- Will I really meet you?
- [Mysterious Voice 2] Who
can say? But we're here now.
- Will you play with me, whoever you are?
- [Mysterious Voice 4] That's why we came.
(Remy laughs)
- [Cuttnal] What do you
mean you called a hearse?
- I'm sorry, but it's almost time for it.
- [Kernagul] Can't you
do anything else for her?
- This hospital is here
to serve the living
and over 200,000 people
a day get sick or injured
in this city alone.
We can't waste a bed on a terminal case
for even one hour.
The dead have no business being here.
It's as simple as that.
And I have final say over
making a life or death call
and that's just the law of the city.
Isn't that right, Surgeon General?
- It's hopeless.
- The Grim Reaper's knocking on the door.
- I give her 30 minutes.
- But there's still a small chance.
- [Doctor] Yes.
There's no point in
isolating her any longer.
You can go in if you want.
(monitor beeping)
(machine whooshing)
(bell chiming)
(ominous music)
- Here they come.
- Well, these guys just
love to race, don't they?
(upbeat music)
(grunting)
(explosion booms)
(gun banging rapidly)
(guns banging rapidly)
(glass shattering)
- Why, you!
Hang on. We're going in!
- Strike team, up top. Keep it moving.
- You got it.
- Here we go!
(all grunting)
(explosion booms)
- That worked perfect.
- Okay, handsome.
Go fly up there and give them a hand.
- Huh?
(explosion booms)
(clocks ticking)
- So, you've made it this far.
Whatever you do won't change anything.
You cannot escape from
this city or your destiny.
- Really?
Well, then if we can't
leave we'll just destroy it
and then we will survive.
Do you read me, Cuttnal? Come in.
(guns banging rapidly)
- Yeah?
Bundle, how's it going on your end?
- [Bundle] It's time. Let them have it.
- All right, lets hit 'em, Kernagul.
Time for the real show, big boy.
- While the kids were showing off
for Remy for the past two days,
we were doing our own thing around town.
(explosions booming)
- Destroying the city changes nothing.
It exists only to form
the fear of destiny.
- Well I'm changing mine.
(gun bangs)
(creature growls)
- [Elder] Nothing can be altered.
It will be as it was.
- No one's coming.
No one's here.
So quiet.
Yeah, I'm going to die.
My body's so cold, so cold.
I'll just give up.
I guess this is all I
could've expected from life.
- Is that me?
No!
It's wrong.
Something's different.
(clocks chiming)
- What's different?
Nothing can save me.
I'm going to die.
- No, no.
That's not me!
(gun bangs)
- But why am I...
Why am I not you?
(creature growls)
(tense music)
(earth crumbling)
- You who dares rebel
against your own destiny.
- I hate you all! I wish you were dead!
(creature growls)
(Remy grunts)
(officer grunting)
- You can't change fate, streetwalker.
(gun bangs)
- Damn. I can't shoot anymore.
- Remy, get ahold of yourself.
We're here with you.
- [Kernagul And Cuttnal] Us too!
- Remy, I never said what day
my letter of fate gave me.
I'll tell you now.
It was yesterday.
But here I am still alive, Remy.
See?
You can beat it too.
- Bundle.
- [Bundle] Do you understand?
- Don't give up, Remy.
Later.
- Be seein' ya.
- I don't know what to say.
- Remy's catchphrase, \"See
ya again\" seems appropriate.
- Why, you overblown piece of...
(both laughing)
(crow squawking)
- Where are you going?
(soft music)
Thanks, guys.
We'll meet again.
We haven't really met
yet but maybe someday.
Yeah, someday.
- [Man] Anybody down there?
- It's me!
It's me, Remy!
- [Man] Down in there?
I don't believe it.
She's still alive.
(monitor beeping)
(machine whooshing)
- Remy, think back.
Think back to when we fought together.
You never gave up then.
Don't you give up now.
- Hang on, Remy.
(Cuttnal groans)
(guns banging rapidly)
(explosions booming)
(wind rustling)
- Well, I'd better go.
(creature growls)
(gun bangs)
(Remy screams)
I won't be beaten.
(uplifting music)
- Why does she fight it even now?
- This is beyond me.
- Because she won't give up.
No matter what.
(gun bangs)
(Remy yelps)
(singing in foreign language)
(Remy yelping)
(gun clicks)
(Remy screams)
No more ammo.
That's it.
(guns banging rapidly)
One shot.
(Remy panting)
I have one shot.
Make it count!
(gun bangs)
(creature roars)
(Remy moans)
(ominous music)
(monitor beeping)
- [Doctor] I'm truly sorry.
- Where are you going?
Fess up, Bundle.
- What do you mean?
- You lied, didn't you?
- [Bundle] Hmm?
- About your letter
saying it was yesterday.
You just said that so I wouldn't give up.
- Perhaps.
But you're still alive, in any case.
And even after they made a grave for you.
Here lies Remy Shimada.
- No kidding.
Bastards.
Bang.
(monitor beeping)
(nurse screams)
(glass shatters)
You forgot.
- What?
- I didn't lose hope that time.
As long as you stay alive,
even if you haven't met them yet,
even if you're not sure you ever will,
you may find people who
will be very special.
- Really?
- Yeah.
(birds chirping)
- I can't believe it's over.
- Yeah, everything is over for us now.
- Guys!
Guys, wait up!
(soft music)
I wanna stay with everyone.
- Beautiful.
Always knew you were.
(Remy laughs)
(uplifting music)