[NARRATOR]
What is the measure of a king?
Are there many prominent
knights in his service?
Are his subjects fruitful,
and his towns thriving?
And above all
else does he, himself,
bear the power of a hero?
These are the measures
by which nations determine
the Ranking of Kings.
[BOJJI sobbing]
[SHIINA] Oh, Prince,
were they bullying you again?
[sobbing continues]
Never you mind them.
You're stronger than they know.
You can persevere
through all of that ugliness.
And then, you must become the
greatest king in all the world.
Promise me.
[laughing]
Tears mingled with sweat
その涙が汗が滲んだ
sono namida ga ase ga nijinda
With your own unique beauty
誰とも違う美しさで
dare to mo chigau utsukushisa de
Smile for me
笑っておくれよ
waratte okureyo
Running out of breath, you're more wonderful than everyone else
息を切らした君は 誰より素敵さ
iki o kirashita kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Ranking of Kings
Almost melting into those listless days
気の抜けた炭酸みたいに
ki no nuketa tansan mitai ni
Feeling drained of energy like a flat soda
微かに気怠い日々に溶けた
kasuka ni kedarui hibi ni toketa
As a duckling, spread your wings,
家鴨の侭で翼を広げて
ahiru no mama de tsubasa o hirogete
dream of becoming a swan and soar through the sky
空を舞う白鳥の夢をみる
sora o mau shiratori no yume o miru
Put in your best effort rather than straying from the path
彷徨うくらいなら 一層味わい尽くしましょ
samayou kurai nara issou ajiwai tsukushimasho
For there's nothing fun about taking shortcuts, right?
近道ばかりじゃ 味気がないでしょ
chikamichi bakarija ajike ga naidesho
You took your time, choosing to take the hard road
道草を食って 泥濘み飲んで
michikusa o kutte nukarumi nonde
But you couldn't get there
でも辿り着けなくて
demo tadori tsukenakute
You keep chasing the sunset as many times as it takes
また何度だって 夕暮れを追いかけるの
mata nando datte yuugure o oikakeruno
Now run ahead
走れ遥か先へ
hashire haruka saki e
Your dirty shoes and footprints will definitely head towards the future
汚れた靴と足跡は 確かに未来へと
yogoreta kutsu to ashiato wa tashika ni mirai e to
Charging forward, running out of breath
今駆けてゆく 息を切らした
ima kaketeyuku iki o kirashita
You're more wonderful than everyone else
君は誰より素敵さ
kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Episode 1
The Prince's New Clothes
[birds twittering]
[BOJJI blowing]
[BOJJI panting]
[KAGE]
Huh? Who the heck are you?
Hey, Get back here!
[BOJJI gasps]
[KAGE] I haven't seen
you around here before.
Who are you, and what's up
with that crown on your head?
Are you trying
to ignore me or what?!
Heh. Fine. I'll make it
easy for ya.
Your money or your life!
What'll it be?!
Uh... Uh, uh―
[KAGE]
Better speak up, little runt!
Your money or your life, I said!
[BOJJI]
Uh... Uh...
[KAGE]
Huh? What's your deal, kid?
You can't talk or somethin'?
And you can't hear, either?
[KAGE] That's gonna
make it kinda hard
to get the idea across.
[BOJJI]
Ah... Ah... Ah...
[KAGE] Guess you're telling me
you don't have any money on ya.
[BOJJI]
Au!
[KAGE] Are you figuring out
what I'm saying by watching
my mouth move?
[BOJJI]
Au!
[KAGE] Now you're asking how I'm
figuring out what you're saying?
Heck if I know,
but I understand you fine.
Hey, don't go
changing the subject!
If ya got no money
then take off your clothes
and leave 'em with me!
Ah!
[KAGE]
Yeah, you play along real nice.
Makes things easier on us
less fortunate types.
It's a good thing
you're doin', kid.
You show some promise,
you know that?
Au!
[KAGE] Now, come back
here tomorrow with
some more fancy clothes!
And hey― Don't tell
anybody about this, all right?
- [BOJJI] Hmm!
- Get outta here.
There are some dumb
kids around nowadays.
[gasping]
[giggling]
What is this about?
It's Prince Bojji,
the king's eldest son.
The prince? That boy?
[TOWNSMAN 1A] My guess is,
he was waylaid by a highwayman
and lost his clothes.
[TRAVELER 1A]
But wasn't he smiling just now?
[TOWNSMAN 1A]
He's an idiot.
Deaf and mute,
to make matters worse.
And to top it off, he can barely
swing a children's sword,
from what I've been told.
A real waste of a prince.
[KAGE]
He's not coming.
[KAGE gasps]
Or maybe...
...he's gonna bring me in!
- [BOJJI] Ahh!
- [KAGE gasps]
[KAGE]
Hmm?
[BOJJI]
Au!
[KAGE groans]
[BOJJI]
Au?
- Hey.
- Ah!
What have you got to
be so happy about, kid?
Ah! Au-wa!
You're happy to have
somebody to talk to?
And that's really all it
takes to make you smile, huh?
[BOJJI]
Hmm! Mm!
I get it.
I guess people don't really
wanna engage with an idiot boy
who can't hear or talk, do they?
[gasps]
Ah, ah, au!
"It's good to meet someone
who understands," you say?
You dunce!
Don't you know when
you're being made fun of?!
What am I gonna
do with this kid?
[BOJJI]
Ah, ah, ah, au.
[KAGE] Hold on. You're
telling me to stay here
so you can bring me even more
of your clothes tomorrow?
Heh. Well, don't expect me
to take orders from you.
What's your name, anyway?
Oh-ee.
- [KAGE] Bojji, huh?
- [BOJJI] Hmm!
I'm Kage.
Aeh. Ah-eh.
Don't strain yourself.
Let's do this
again tomorrow, Bojji.
[BOJJI]
Ah!
[KAGE]
Never met anyone like that.
But I'll get quite a bit
for his clothes.
Might as well stick with it.
[BOJJI]
Ah-eh!
Ah, ah!
[chuckling]
Ah. Eh! Ah. Eh. Ah-eh!
[giggles]
Ah! Ah, ah, ah!
Oh, wow, you're
the prince livin' in
that great big castle.
That means you're
gonna be king someday.
Wah! Ah, ah, ah!
[KAGE] You seriously
believe you're gonna be
the greatest king in the world?
[laughs]
You've got none of what it takes
to be a great king, fool!
How're you gonna lead
people when you're deaf
and don't talk?
You really are some kind
of idiot, aren't you?
[BOJJI growls]
Ah-em, ahm, aum!
[KAGE]
Eh. And even if all that's true,
you're still gonna
be a great king?
Yeah, whatever.
You go become a great king,
and make the world
a more fun place to live.
Au!
[KAGE] Heh, heh.
I'll be lookin' forward to it.
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmuring]
[KAGE] Sure enough,
he's the butt of all the jokes.
'Course, that's really
'cause of me.
[TOWNSWOMAN 1A]
I've seen him out of his clothes
every day, lately.
[TOWNSMAN 1B]
Who knows what will become of us
if he ends up our next king.
Wah!
[GIRL 1A] Hey. Why don't
you have any clothes?
[TOWNSMAN 1C]
Did she just say that...?
[BOYS]
Where are they?!
[TOWNSMAN 1D]
He can't hear them...
[TOWNSMAN 1E]
You three!
The prince isn't able
to hear anything.
- Whoa!
- He has ears!
Why not?!
Some people have ears,
but still can't hear.
Then he can't hear us
if we say mean stuff!
- Ya big dummy!
- [laughs]
[TOWNSMAN 1E]
Easy, now...
Wow...
[GIRL 1A] So, you...
Can't you say anything?
Ah, heh-woh?
"Wah-hewoh!"
- [laughs]
- [GIRL 1A] You poor boy.
- Wait, you!
Hey, don't run away!
If you can't talk,
then just say you can't talk!
[KAGE]
There's a sharp one.
No way...
This is where
the little runt lives?
I dunno why,
but that kinda bugs me.
[SOLDIER 1A]
He came back here naked again.
It's sad to see.
[SOLDIER 1B]
He doesn't even understand
how big of a fool he is.
[sighs]
Ignorance is bliss.
[HILING] You walked out
among the public, undressed?
And what, pray tell, compelled
you to do that, Prince Bojji?
Queen Hilling
Mother of Second Prince Daida
Justice Minister Sandeo
[SANDEO] Most likely, the prince
was accosted by highwaymen.
Big Four
'Swordmaster' Domas
[HILING] How could
something like that happen
Prince Bojji's swordsmanship tutor
to one of our princes? Pathetic!
Big Four
'Spear of the King' Apis
'Shield of the Queen' Drusi
[HILING]
Domas.
[DOMAS]
Aye?
The culprits will
be put to death.
Go out and apprehend them.
It shall be done.
[gasps]
[HILING]
You say I've misunderstood?
You put yourself in
this state for some game?
What sort of game is that?!
Your actions will tarnish the
dignity of this royal family,
and what's more, they'll disrupt
the harmony of our kingdom!
Normally, these offenses
would cost you your head!
But no, there is hardly a need.
Clearly, this boy
is not fit to be a king.
[DOMAS]
Oh...
Don't translate that!
It couldn't be clearer
that Daida is more apt
for the throne.
He appears to be rather
shocked at what I just said.
I thought he couldn't hear me.
That is our understanding.
[HILING]
Hmph. Let's be off.
How can it be that he
is next in line for the throne,
and not Daida?
Does merit count for nothing?
You! Straighten that uniform
or lose your head!
[SOLDIER 1C]
F-Forgive me, Your Majesty!
[KAGE] Either her corset's
cinched up way too tight,
or she's just crazy.
Is that a queen?
[DOMAS]
Prince.
The king was hoping
to speak with you.
Please go see him
as soon as you're dressed.
[BOJJI whimpering]
[KAGE]
Huh...?
[whimpering continues]
[BOJJI sniffs]
[KAGE]
This kid...
He's putting on a brave face,
pretending not to understand.
[KAGE]
Hold on. Which way did he go?
[KAGE gasps]
[whimpers]
Big Four
'Snake Handler' Bebin
[BEBIN] You're a member
of the shadow clan.
Second Prince Daida's swordsmanship tutor
That despicable
clan of assassins.
I was told they'd been
wiped out to the very last.
[BEBIN]
You're still just a child.
[knocking]
[BOSSE]
Enter.
[BOJJI grunts]
7th in the Ranking of Kings
King Boss
There you are...
...Prince.
[NARRATOR]
The attack came without warning.
[ORCS roaring]
[NARRATOR] Even through
their grave losses,
the villagers continued
to fight with all they had.
[gasps]
What is that...?
[NARRATOR] Until, at last,
the land itself was engulfed by
the monstrous horde and the
villagers cursed their fate.
[MEN gasping]
[NARRATOR]
But then, from out of nowhere,
a great man strode forth...
[BOSSE growls]
[NARRATOR] ...and fought back
with a ferocity beyond words.
[bellows]
[BOSSE sighs]
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[NARRATOR] And so began
the Kingdom of Bosse.
[BOSSE] Bojji. I'm told you've
made a habit of wandering about
the town in a state of undress.
Premier Sori
What is the meaning of this?
We of the royal family
must show the bearing
our subjects expect of us.
[coughs]
[grunts]
Were you attacked by bandits?
Or perhaps simply being bullied?
In any case, you are ultimately
responsible for being
in that situation at all―
[coughing]
King Bosse!
[BOSSE]
Calm yourself.
My Bojji. You are the son
of the late first queen.
I adore you more
than I can bear.
And yet...
When I think of what shall
become of our country
when I am gone, my heart weeps.
Your hands are soft and weak,
and Daida's are swollen
with the callouses
from his great efforts.
Take heart. I have left your
training in the hands of Domas,
the most capable
swordsman in the land.
You can surely become stronger.
Domas.
[DOMAS]
Majesty?
You are to be more rigorous
in teaching the prince
swordsmanship.
[DOMAS]
Aye.
And you must learn it well,
my dear son.
Now go.
[KAGE panting]
[KAGE whines]
[BEBIN] So, who hired
you to come here,
and who did they
hire you to kill?
If you don't answer...
[KAGE]
I'm not here to kill anyone!
I already told you
I don't do that!
[grunts, yells]
[BEBIN]
Assassination has always been
the shadow clan's livelihood.
They were once the chosen
assassins for the Kingdom of Bo,
and when they'd pledge
loyalty to a ruler,
they'd never betray them.
Don't you dare talk about that!
But it seems something changed.
They tried to kill their king,
and in return,
they were eradicated,
isn't that right?
[BEBIN]
So?
You'd better start talking!
[BEBIN] Tsk. Hiding in
the shadows, I see.
[BEBIN] Be on alert,
though I don't suspect
he poses a real threat.
[BOJJI grunting]
[DOMAS sighs]
[bellows]
[DOMAS panting]
[DAIDA]
Going wild, are we?
Why, good day to you,
Prince Daida.
Second Prince Daida
So. How is my brother?
Is he showing improvement
in his training?
How about a brief spar
so I can see what he can do?
[DOMAS] Hmm. Sorry, but I don't
believe that would be prudent.
Then instead, Domas,
may I spar with you?
[DOMAS grunts]
With me?
Yes! It surely wouldn't
do any harm, would it?
[DOMAS]
Well... Perhaps.
[DOMAS] I heard he easily
defeated the top captain
in the Order of Bebin.
And that made him cocky.
[DOMAS] Against
my inclination, I accept.
[DOMAS]
If he insists...
...I can take him down a peg.
[gasps]
[DOMAS]
That intensity...
He's the spitting
image of King Bosse!
[DAIDA snarls]
[DOMAS gasps]
[DAIDA grunts]
Raugh!
[yelling]
[grunting]
[DOMAS]
He's... He's outstanding!
[gasps]
[DOMAS]
How do you like this?!
C'mon, more!
[DAIDA grunting]
[growls]
[yells]
[grunting]
[BOJJI whines]
[DAIDA gasps]
[wheezes]
[growls]
[snarls]
[DOMAS]
You are magnificently skilled!
[DAIDA growls]
[growls]
[DOMAS]
He will only grow stronger.
He wields the sword like a king!
I want to teach this boy!
[gasps]
Prince Bojji?
[DAIDA]
Huh? What's this, now?
You mean to fight me, too?
[KAGE]
For cryin' out loud.
I follow the little
twerp back here
and look what
I get tangled up in.
I gotta get outta
this creepy place and―
[SOLDIER 1D]
Hey, did you hear?
Word is that Prince Bojji and
Prince Daida are having a fight.
Let's go watch!
[KAGE]
Him... in a fight?
[SOLDIERS murmuring]
What's this commotion?
Someone explain.
[DORSHE] It would seem the two
princes are about to fight.
[HILING sighs] That is an
absolutely preposterous notion.
[DOMAS] Prince Bojji is hardly
a match for Prince Daida.
What could he be thinking?
Hey. Who do you expect to win?
You're not seriously
asking, are you?
Prince Daida took on Bohen in
a match and humiliated him.
A top captain.
He resigned from
the order in shame.
True enough.
But once, before...
[gasps]
Ah!
[HOKURO] I guess we'll find out
for sure during this bout.
Right then.
The match will hereby commence.
Are the combatants
ready to fight?
It would appear Domas's
pupil has challenged yours
to a contest of swordplay.
[BEBIN] Hmph. Well, we all know
the outcome is hardly in doubt.
Be warned, Brother―
I won't hold back.
[BOJJI]
Au.
[DOMAS]
Begin!
[yells]
[DAIDA growls]
[grunting]
[HOKURO gasps]
[HOKURO]
I knew it!
That time wasn't a fluke!
[HOKURO]
It was his own ability!
[DAIDA grunts]
[yells]
[grunting]
[BOJJI]
Ah!
Mm!
[gasping]
[SOLDIER 1E]
He hit him!
[SOLDIER 1F]
He dodged and countered!
[KAGE]
Hey, not bad!
You're not bad at all, Bojji!
Please don't leave me alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないでよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaideyo
Since when did I start getting used to
いつから重たい荷物を持つ
itsukara omotai nimotsu o motsu
carrying a heavy burden day after day
日々に慣れてしまっていたんだろう
hibi ni nareteshimatteitan darou
Don't worry and set aside all your difficulties
難しいことは後回しでいいから
muzukashii koto wa atomawashide iikara
Night awaits me when I'm lonely
孤独なボクを夜が待つ
kodoku na boku o yoru ga matsu
Please don't make me feel lonely anymore
寂しい思いはもうボクにはさせないでよ
sabishii omoi wa mou boku ni wa sasenaideyo
Please don't seek solitude
思い出した夜を
omoidashita yoru o
when you remember that night
どうかひとりぼっちとは呼ばないで
douka hitori bocchito wa yobanaide
If you are weak
あなたが弱いのなら
anata ga yowai no nara
I'll show my weakness
ボクの弱さも見せるから
boku no yowasa mo miserukara
And if you pretend to be strong,
あなたが強がるのならば
anata ga tsuyogaru nonaraba
I'll gently embrace your weakness
キミの弱さをそっと抱きしめるよ
kimi no yowasa o sotto dakishimeruyo
I won't leave you alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaiyo