[KAGE]
This guy's name is Bojji.
He can't talk and he can't hear,
and to make matters worse,
he's too naïve and kindhearted
for his own good.
But his fancy clothes caught my
attention, and before I knew it,
I'd followed him straight into
the predicament I'm in now.
As if society hadn't thrown
enough grief my way,
someone in town figured out I
was a member of the Shadow Clan,
who used to work
as killers for hire.
If only I'd done the smart
thing and run away.
But then I heard that Bojji
would be sparring with
his younger brother Daida, who's
already a skilled swordsman.
And for some reason, I decided
to stick around and watch.
Tears mingled with sweat
その涙が汗が滲んだ
sono namida ga ase ga nijinda
With your own unique beauty
誰とも違う美しさで
dare to mo chigau utsukushisa de
Smile for me
笑っておくれよ
waratte okureyo
Running out of breath, you're more wonderful than everyone else
息を切らした君は 誰より素敵さ
iki o kirashita kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Ranking of Kings
Almost melting into those listless days
気の抜けた炭酸みたいに
ki no nuketa tansan mitai ni
Feeling drained of energy like a flat soda
微かに気怠い日々に溶けた
kasuka ni kedarui hibi ni toketa
As a duckling, spread your wings,
家鴨の侭で翼を広げて
ahiru no mama de tsubasa o hirogete
dream of becoming a swan and soar through the sky
空を舞う白鳥の夢をみる
sora o mau shiratori no yume o miru
Put in your best effort rather than straying from the path
彷徨うくらいなら 一層味わい尽くしましょ
samayou kurai nara issou ajiwai tsukushimasho
For there's nothing fun about taking shortcuts, right?
近道ばかりじゃ 味気がないでしょ
chikamichi bakarija ajike ga naidesho
You took your time, choosing to take the hard road
道草を食って 泥濘み飲んで
michikusa o kutte nukarumi nonde
But you couldn't get there
でも辿り着けなくて
demo tadori tsukenakute
You keep chasing the sunset as many times as it takes
また何度だって 夕暮れを追いかけるの
mata nando datte yuugure o oikakeruno
Now run ahead
走れ遥か先へ
hashire haruka saki e
Your dirty shoes and footprints will definitely head towards the future
汚れた靴と足跡は 確かに未来へと
yogoreta kutsu to ashiato wa tashika ni mirai e to
Charging forward, running out of breath
今駆けてゆく 息を切らした
ima kaketeyuku iki o kirashita
You're more wonderful than everyone else
君は誰より素敵さ
kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Episode 2
The Prince and Kage
[KAGE panting]
[SHADOW CLAN whimpering]
[screaming]
[KAGE panting]
[KAGE'S MOTHER gasps]
Hide!
You can't hide forever!
Hey!
[KAGE'S MOTHER] There's someone
from the Light Clan.
Kage, I need you to keep
running by yourself, now.
[KAGE gasps]
What about you?
Your mom shouldn't have
any trouble with these men,
but I can't fight them unless I
know you're out of harm's way,
so you have to keep running.
I'll catch up with you
in the toxic forest up ahead.
Do you understand?
[KAGE whimpers]
Mm...
[KAGE'S MOTHER] You are so
precious to me, my sweet Kage.
[KAGE sighs]
[KAGE'S MOTHER]
Right. Now go.
Quickly!
[KAGE]
Hurry, okay?
[KAGE'S MOTHER]
I'll crush them!
White light!
[KAGE'S MOTHER gasps]
Found you.
One of them got away.
Kill it!
[KAGE'S MOTHER]
No, you don't!
Your kind are powerful
in the shadows,
but quite weak once exposed.
Rather bold of you.
[KAGE'S MOTHER] Geslan,
what poison have you whispered
in the king's ear?
I hardly see any call
for such accusations.
Take a look, my dear.
I can offer a painless death,
so save us the trouble
and keep still.
[KAGE panting]
Where's the toxic forest...?
Still that far?
[panting]
[KAGE]
M-Mama!
[KAGE gasps]
[GESLAN] Goodness,
but you're a stubborn one!
[KAGE'S MOTHER]
I hope you escaped, Kage...
Mama won't be catching up...
[GESLAN] I suppose you
were trying to buy time for
that brat of yours, but I
believe it was already captured
by another patrol.
[KAGE'S MOTHER shrieks]
[slashing]
[KNIGHT 2A] My, if it isn't
the young countess, Poise.
Did a shadow clan child
just pass by here, miss?
[KNIGHT 2A]
What a creepy little girl.
Fled to the forest, as expected.
You have our thanks.
[GESLAN]
Did you finish it yet?
[KNIGHT 2A]
No.
It appears to have fled
into the toxic forest, sir.
[GESLAN growls]
Get after it, then.
[HORSE whinnies]
[KAGE gasps]
Mama..!
- [shrieks]
- [POISE gasps]
- [shrieking continues]
- [POISE wails]
[SERVANT 2A gasps]
What could be the matter?!
Please, be on your way, sirs!
You're frightening
the young lady!
[KNIGHT 2A]
We beg your pardon.
Lord Geslan, let us go.
- [GESLAN] Tch!
- [wailing continues]
[KAGE wailing]
As servants of King Bo,
we offer our aid,
though this is all
we have to give.
You'll reach another kingdom
further down this path.
There, you will find safety.
[KAGE whimpers]
Thank you very much...
Good luck to you!
[POISE]
Do you think he'll be all right?
Although the Shadow Clan
is fallen,
their strength is sure
to see him through.
Now, we must be on
our way too, I'm afraid.
[KAGE whimpering]
[stomach growling]
[stomach growling continues]
[KAGE whimpering]
- [stomach growling]
- [KAGE groans]
[KAGE'S MOTHER] Here, Kage! I
have a birthday present for you!
[KAGE]
Really?! Oh, boy!
Ah! Ah!
- Thank you, Mama!
- [KAGE'S MOTHER chuckles]
[KAGE whimpers]
[KAGE] Can I trade you
this for an apple...?
If you wanna buy
something, bring money!
[TOWNSWOMAN 2A]
I'll take four of these, please.
Of course!
[TOWNSWOMAN 2B gasps]
Get back here right now!
Hey!
[KAGE grunts]
[whines]
[blows thudding]
[KAGE gasps]
[TOWNSMAN 2A]
Hmm.
[KAGE whimpering]
What are you lookin' at?!
I give you food,
I expect you to eat it!
You got a problem with that?!
[KAGE whimpers]
No, sir...
[TOWNSMAN 2A]
Come to think of it...
I might just need you to
start bringin' in some coin
for my trouble.
Get inside here and
open the door for me.
You can do that, right?
[KAGE]
Mm. Yes, sir...
Nicely done.
Ah...!
Perfect!
[laughs]
You pulled it off, shadow buddy!
[TOWNSMAN 2A]
There we go...
Good work, bud.
Your cut.
[KAGE]
Huh?
Ah...
[snoring]
[KAGE sighs]
[TOWNSMAN 2A] Damn it,
how could I have lost again?!
I won't stand for it!
[gasps]
Ah―
Ah?
Huh?
Hmm...
[chuckles]
[KAGE snoring softly]
[KAGE] Mama, you and
the others are some kinda
super powerful
assassins, aren't you?
So tell me about all the scary
bad guys you've gotten rid of!
[KAGE'S MOTHER]
Let's see...
We kill whoever we're
ordered to, I suppose.
Women, children,
the old and infirm.
[KAGE]
Uh! You're joking!
[KAGE'S MOTHER]
It's the truth.
That's why we couldn't object
if someone were to try and kill
all of us, down the line.
[KAGE]
But why do you do that stuff...?
[KAGE'S MOTHER] Hmm... Perhaps
it's these bodies of ours.
They're perfectly suited
to doing awful things.
[KAGE'S MOTHER] But listen...
We do everything we can
in order to serve the interests
of the people who need us most,
and that is the light
that guides us.
[KAGE'S MOTHER gasps]
Oh no! They're coming!
- Wake up, Kage!
- [footsteps approaching]
[KAGE grunts, gasps]
[SOLDIER 2A gasps]
There!
It just slipped out the window!
After it! Hurry!
[TOWNSMAN 2A chuckles]
[SOLDIER 2B] It's gone.
We'll never find it in the dark.
[TOWNSMAN 2A snoring]
[knocking]
Who's here knockin'
at this hour?
Huh? Huh?!
You? What are you
doing back here?!
[KAGE whimpers]
I'm done with you!
Get lost already!
Shoo! Scat!
[KAGE whines]
[PATRONS chattering]
[TOWNSMAN 2A gulping]
[TOWNSMAN 2B grunts]
[laughing]
[yelps]
Please, don't hurt me!
[TOWNSMAN 2A] You should watch
what you're doing!
- [blows thudding]
- [TOWNSMAN 2B grunting]
- [slice]
- [TOWNSMAN 2A yelps]
[TOWNSMAN 2A whimpering]
[groaning]
Oi.
If that's not a
pitiful way to go...
[KAGE whimpering]
[TOWNSMAN 2A sighs]
[KAGE gasps, whimpers]
[PATRONS murmuring]
- [TOWNSMAN 2E] Get outta here!
- [KAGE gasps]
[TOWNSMEN grunting]
[KAGE whimpering]
[KAGE chuckles]
Scored big today.
This haul oughta keep me
fed for a good long while.
Who the heck are you?
Hey, get back here!
[BOJJI]
Ah!
I haven't seen you
around here before.
[KAGE] Why did I put myself
in danger just to come back
for this little runt?
[DOMAS]
Begin!
[grunts]
[yells]
- [KAGE gasps]
- Ah!
[grunting]
[KAGE gasps]
Ah!
[DAIDA grunts]
[BOJJI]
Au!
[KAGE]
You're not bad at all, Bojji!
[DOMAS] I never realized
Prince Bojji was so capable!
[DOMAS]
But now...
[DAIDA growls]
Ah!
[grunting]
Ridiculous!
[gasps]
[growls]
[grunting]
[KAGE]
Yes, Bojji!
You can tell what people
are saying just by
watching their lips!
Your eyes and
your insight are sharp!
Prince Daida appears on
the verge of defeat,
just what do you make of this?
You think he's losing?
He clearly seems
unable to defend himself.
[laughs] Prince Bojji lacks
the strength to land
a decisive blow, and if,
by some miracle, he should win,
it will prove him
unworthy of the crown.
[SOLDIER 2C] Say, doesn't
Prince Bojji's way of fighting
seem a bit dirty?
[SOLDIER 2D]
True. Cowardly, even.
[SOLDIER 2E]
Underhanded.
[SOLDIER 2F]
It disgusts me.
[SOLDIER 2G]
He's a sneak.
[KAGE]
That's it! You got it, Bojji!
[BEBIN] To the those watching,
It seems he's making sport
of his opponent's
desperate efforts,
and that's turning
them against him.
But this kind of trickery
is the only way for someone
so weak to survive.
[BEBIN] So what will
you do, Prince Bojji?
[DAIDA growls]
Damn!
You fight dirty, Brother!
[gasps]
[KAGE]
What? What was that?
Surely you needn't
say it so coldly, Domas.
Either way,
it needed to be said.
[yells]
[BOJJI groaning]
- [DAIDA growls]
- [coughs]
[KAGE]
Hey, why'd you quit dodging?!
- [DAIDA grunting]
- [BOJJI groaning]
[DAIDA panting]
[growls]
- [grunting]
- [blows cracking]
Somebody, stop him!
- [grunting continues]
- [blows thudding]
[DAIDA panting]
[BOJJI whimpering]
[KAGE gasps]
Bojji...
[SOLDIERS murmuring]
[DAIDA growls]
- [KAGE whimpering]
- [DAIDA yells]
[blows thudding]
[KAGE whimpering]
- Stop...
- [DAIDA growls]
[KAGE]
Stop it!
[DOMAS]
Hmm?
Apeas...
Match over!
Prince Daida has prevailed!
Someone get him a doctor, now!
[KAGE gasps]
Bojji...
Apeas. I know what
you're trying to tell me.
I'm sorry,
but please understand.
Shame on you for using
such underhanded
tactics, Big Brother.
[DAIDA] Hmph. Now you can
never handle a sword again.
What exactly did
Domas say to him?
Ah. "That is not
the swordsmanship of a king.
The two of you
must trade blows."
[laughs] Then everything is
playing out just as predicted.
Excellent.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Welcome back.
Yes. It would seem
my path to the throne
is clearing up quickly,
just as you said it would.
[BOJJI panting]
[DOMAS] He shows great skill at
evading his opponent's blows,
but even with a short sword,
he can't strike back decisively,
so he can't defeat his enemy.
And he was born under
a star that won't let him
grow stronger. I truly pity him.
I shall return.
[KAGE]
So that was Domas?
I know his type.
You can never count
on guys like that.
[panting]
[SOLDIER 2H]
That's dirty swordplay!
How cowardly!
[DOMAS] "This is not the
swordsmanship of a king."
[BOJJI whimpers]
[KAGE]
Hey, where you going?
You can't get out
of bed like that!
[BOJJI whimpers]
[sword clanks]
[panting]
[groaning]
[yells]
[KAGE]
Bojji...
[BOJJI whimpering]
[yells]
[sobs softly]
[whimpering]
[sobbing]
Au.
[KAGE] You've got nothing
to be embarrassed about.
I was watching that match.
You won that fight and
made it look easy, okay?
Hold your head up high, kid!
You were doing just fine
fighting your own way,
so don't let any of
those fools tell you not to!
[gasps]
Au, au!
Listen― I'm not
taking anything else
from you anymore, got it?
I don't know how
this is gonna sound,
and I get that
it's outta nowhere...
[groans]
I just--!
I'm on your side, all right?!
No matter what happens!
[BOJJI gasps]
[whimpering]
[KAGE]
And I mean what I'm saying.
I've got your back
from now on, Bojji.
Always.
[BOJJI whimpering]
Ah...
Please don't leave me alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないでよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaideyo
Since when did I start getting used to
いつから重たい荷物を持つ
itsukara omotai nimotsu o motsu
carrying a heavy burden day after day
日々に慣れてしまっていたんだろう
hibi ni nareteshimatteitan darou
Don't worry and set aside all your difficulties
難しいことは後回しでいいから
muzukashii koto wa atomawashide iikara
Night awaits me when I'm lonely
孤独なボクを夜が待つ
kodoku na boku o yoru ga matsu
Please don't make me feel lonely anymore
寂しい思いはもうボクにはさせないでよ
sabishii omoi wa mou boku ni wa sasenaideyo
Please don't seek solitude
思い出した夜を
omoidashita yoru o
when you remember that night
どうかひとりぼっちとは呼ばないで
douka hitori bocchito wa yobanaide
If you are weak
あなたが弱いのなら
anata ga yowai no nara
I'll show my weakness
ボクの弱さも見せるから
boku no yowasa mo miserukara
And if you pretend to be strong,
あなたが強がるのならば
anata ga tsuyogaru nonaraba
I'll gently embrace your weakness
キミの弱さをそっと抱きしめるよ
kimi no yowasa o sotto dakishimeruyo
I won't leave you alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaiyo