[KAGE] Guess you're stuck
here for a while.
I'll check up on
you tomorrow, all right?
See ya.
[KAGE]
Hmm?
[door creaks]
[KAGE]
Is that...?
- [HILING sighs]
- [KAGE gasps]
[KAGE]
No... She wouldn't!
[HILING grunts, groans]
[groaning continues]
[panting]
[HILING groaning]
[KAGE chuckles]
The moon is pretty tonight.
[humming]
[BEBIN] Still skulking
about inside the castle?
[BEBIN] Then you've
forfeited your opportunity
to leave here alive.
[KAGE]
Oh, no!
[grunting]
[gasps]
[KAGE gasps]
[KAGE whimpers]
Tears mingled with sweat
その涙が汗が滲んだ
sono namida ga ase ga nijinda
With your own unique beauty
誰とも違う美しさで
dare to mo chigau utsukushisa de
Smile for me
笑っておくれよ
waratte okureyo
Running out of breath, you're more wonderful than everyone else
息を切らした君は 誰より素敵さ
iki o kirashita kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Ranking of Kings
Almost melting into those listless days
気の抜けた炭酸みたいに
ki no nuketa tansan mitai ni
Feeling drained of energy like a flat soda
微かに気怠い日々に溶けた
kasuka ni kedarui hibi ni toketa
As a duckling, spread your wings,
家鴨の侭で翼を広げて
ahiru no mama de tsubasa o hirogete
dream of becoming a swan and soar through the sky
空を舞う白鳥の夢をみる
sora o mau shiratori no yume o miru
Put in your best effort rather than straying from the path
彷徨うくらいなら 一層味わい尽くしましょ
samayou kurai nara issou ajiwai tsukushimasho
For there's nothing fun about taking shortcuts, right?
近道ばかりじゃ 味気がないでしょ
chikamichi bakarija ajike ga naidesho
You took your time, choosing to take the hard road
道草を食って 泥濘み飲んで
michikusa o kutte nukarumi nonde
But you couldn't get there
でも辿り着けなくて
demo tadori tsukenakute
You keep chasing the sunset as many times as it takes
また何度だって 夕暮れを追いかけるの
mata nando datte yuugure o oikakeruno
Now run ahead
走れ遥か先へ
hashire haruka saki e
Your dirty shoes and footprints will definitely head towards the future
汚れた靴と足跡は 確かに未来へと
yogoreta kutsu to ashiato wa tashika ni mirai e to
Charging forward, running out of breath
今駆けてゆく 息を切らした
ima kaketeyuku iki o kirashita
You're more wonderful than everyone else
君は誰より素敵さ
kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Episode 3
The New King
[sobbing]
Oh, Father...
[HILING sobs]
I shall now read the will
of the late king.
The successor to the throne...
[SANDEO]
...is to be Prince Bojji.
[GROUP gasping]
Absurd!
[HILING sighs]
- [DORSHE] What's that?
- [gasping]
[gasping, yelling]
A monster!
[gasping]
[DEMON 3A]
Hmm...
[gasping]
[laughter]
[DAIDA gasps]
[GROUP gasping]
Explain this, Magic Mirror!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Prince Daida. Welcome back.
What happened?!
My brother's been
chosen to become king!
[MAGIC MIRROR] Yet the
throne shall belong to you,
Prince Daida.
But how?
It's all proceeding in full
accordance with my plan.
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmuring]
[TOWNSMAN 3A sighs]
So First Prince Bojji's
really gonna become
our next king?
I'd feel safer with
Prince Daida on the throne.
By will of the late King Bosse,
we hereby announce
his successor.
[DOMAS growls]
[SORII]
Your new king...
...is Prince Daida!
- [gasps]
- [TOWNSPEOPLE cheering]
[HILING] This cannot stand.
I move to veto the king's will.
- [gasping]
- But― Your Majesty!
You'd defy his wishes and keep
Prince Bojji from the throne?
Do you truly believe Bojji is
capable of serving as king?
[DOMAS gasps]
The will though...
To simply disregard
the late king's mandate...
After what we witnessed
on his deathbed,
how could we follow his will?
[gasping]
[groaning]
[HILING] The seven of us
shall vote to determine
the successor to the throne.
All of you, eyes closed
and hands forward.
Whoever believes Bojji is
capable of serving as king,
raise up your finger now.
[HILING]
Open your eyes.
[gasping]
The two of us are opposed
to his succession.
By a vote of five to two,
Daida shall become king.
Why, Domas?!
How could you?!
[TOWNSPEOPLE cheering]
[BOJJI]
Uh...
[BOJJI whimpering]
[HILING gasps]
[SOLDIER 3A gasps]
Prince Bojji!
[BOJJI whimpering]
[sobbing]
[wails]
[KAGE groaning]
Ow...
You bastard...
[groans]
Just stay... outta my way!
[yells]
[KAGE]
No time to hurt. Gotta run!
[gasps]
[BEBIN] It takes a great deal
of grit to carve through
your own flesh,
and I commend you for that.
Sadly... I can't let you leave.
[KAGE gasps]
[BEBIN] Now, who sent
you to this castle,
and who did they want killed?
This is your last chance.
Answer now or die.
[KAGE] I told you before,
I'm not here to kill anybody!
All I wanna do is help
Bojji any way I can!
To help Prince Bojji...?
Prince Bojji.
Ah! Au!
Do you know the creature
I've drawn here?
[BEBIN]
You call him a friend? I see.
Your friend has sent me
to deliver a message.
He has just set off
on a journey.
He said you will never
be seeing each other again.
That is what I came
here to tell you.
By your leave.
[BOJJI whimpers]
[KAGE] Listen.
I'm on your side, all right?
No matter what happens!
He has set off on a journey.
You won't see him again.
[BOJJI gasps]
Ah. Aeh!
[BEBIN]
You've summoned me, King Daida?
I have decided.
I'll stand atop
the Ranking of Kings!
And therefore, I must
eliminate any unstable elements
within my court.
Apeas and Sandeo were the ones
who voted against me, correct?
[BEBIN gasps]
How could you know that?
[DAIDA] Hmph. Please,
give me a bit of credit.
I want those two disposed of!
Dead men tell no tales.
[BEBIN] I doubt this was
King Daida's idea.
What seeds has that Magic Mirror
been planting in his mind?
[gasping]
[GATEKEEPER 3B]
Prince Bojji!
Aeh! Aeh!
[gasps]
[grunts]
Ah!
[groaning]
Aeh!
[BOJJI gasps]
Mitsumata
It has been far too long,
Prince Bojji.
Aeh!
Indeed, Master Bebin, has
apprehended the creature
you now seek.
[gasps]
A-eh! Ah, eh, eh!
I have never forgotten
the debt which I owe you,
and yet, even for your sake,
I cannot ignore the debt
I owe to my master.
[BOJJI]
Au! Au-au-eh!
[sobbing]
[MITSUMATA] Prince Boji,
your friend is safe.
Ah!
He and Master Bebin
arranged a deal.
He has gone off on a journey
to fulfill an important duty.
Though I can say no more
of this to you,
I can offer you an assurance.
You are held precious
in the sight of so many,
and you must not forget that.
[BOJJI]
Euah...
[MITSUMATA]
Now, please run along.
I'd rather Master Bebin
not learn of this.
[BOJJI]
Au!
[BEBIN grunts]
[APEAS groaning]
Are you acting on
King Daida's orders?
[BEBIN]
Hmph.
[BEBIN grunts]
Hmph!
[APEAS]
Tch!
[growls]
- [APEAS grunts]
- [BEBIN groans]
[BEBIN rasping]
King Daida...
[groans]
[APEAS] I will see
Prince Bojji become king...
...Your Majesty.
Be prepared.
[HILING] You asked Apeas
and Sandeo to resign?
[DAIDA] The Spear of
the King is not needed.
I still have Bebin
in my service,
and I'm told that you and Sandeo
have found yourselves
at odds lately, as well.
[HILING] Even so, I worry
that you've acted in haste.
Put it aside for now.
What is to be done
about Brother?
"What is to be done"?
I don't follow.
This matter is giving me
rather a hard time.
[HILING sighs]
[DAIDA] Ideally, we could
have him retired to―
That won't do!
[DAIDA grunts]
Mentally speaking,
Prince Bojji is only a child.
I have an obligation
to educate him.
[DAIDA groans] That could be a
miserable experience for him,
wouldn't you say?
I'm certain he would be fine.
There's no need
to trouble yourself.
You are the king
and should act as such.
[DAIDA]
Hmph. Wise words.
I shall heed them.
[DEMON 3A mumbling]
[KAGE]
Bojji!
[HILING]
Preposterous!
Au! Ah-ooh-eeh! Au! Au-eh!
There will be no such journey.
I won't allow it!
What do you think you can
do under your own power?
Ah!
[HILING] Your ears are deaf
and your body is frail,
and you embarrass yourself every
time you step out in public!
You need to stay put in
the castle and behave yourself!
You're the king's older brother,
and thus―
you have a duty to the
royal family and to Daida.
Ah...
[BOJJI whimpers softly]
[HILING]
Wha― Ah! Bu―
Ugh...
[BOJJI]
Ah...
Prince Bojji, on direct
orders from Queen Hiling,
we are not to let you
leave your chambers.
Ah-eh. Ah.
[gulps]
Bojji? I'm coming in now.
Ah!
[shrieks]
Have you gone mad?!
Here, Dorshe!
Ah!
[HILING sighs]
Au! Eh! Augh!
Stop that!
Are you trying to get killed?!
[shrieks]
[DORSHE gasps]
[HILING wailing]
Au!
Ah!
[HILING gasps]
[HILING]
Bojji!
[panting]
[gasps]
[snarls]
[HILING snarls]
[HILING groaning]
[gasps]
[groaning continues]
[HILING gulping]
[sighs]
[groaning]
[panting]
[BOJJI whimpers]
- [gasps]
- [BOJJI] Ah!
Au, au, ah!
[DORSCHE]
Stay with me, Queen Hiling!
What is he wearing?
[MAIDS giggling]
That could be a miserable
experience for him,
wouldn't you say?
[BOJJI]
Au...
I'm Hiling.
It's so lovely to meet you.
Starting now,
I'm going to be your mom.
Huh?
Well, goodness.
That was rude.
Sadly, the prince hasn't
opened his heart to anyone
since the late queen's passing,
so it's to be expected.
It's nothing against you.
[HILING]
I see...
Hello, Prince.
What have you got there?
Oh!
Ah! Prince!
I brought some... cake.
[BOJJI babbling]
P-Prince, you're dripping!
[sighs]
[BOJJI gasps]
[screams]
[HILING]
Mm? Ah!
[screaming]
- [HILING snarls]
- Ah? Au, au!
[wailing]
[HILING grunts]
[groaning]
[BOJJI]
Ah, eh! Au! Au-au! Yeh!
[HILING chuckles]
- Au, au! Au!
- Yes, yes.
[MAID 3C] Prince Bojji has
been growing quite attached
to the young queen
lately, hasn't he?
Bojji. Before long, you're going
to become a big brother.
[HILING]
See? You felt it move!
[chuckles]
Shh.
There's hardly a need.
Clearly, this boy
is not fit to be a king.
Preposterous!
I won't allow it!
[gasps]
I shall permit you
to take your journey.
- Ah--!
- However!
You will be accompanied by two
others. One is the Swordmaster,
Domas.
And here is the other.
Your name, if you would?
It's Hokuro! Sorry!
He's the one soldier who wished
to join you, and he can sign.
Hokuro will tend to
your personal care
during your travels.
You shall see
my family at their home
and offer your respects.
Then you will
promptly return here.
Wh-What does that mean?
If you understand what
I'm saying, then respond.
- [BOJJI] Mwah.
- [gasps]
E-Enough dawdling! Get ready!
[BOJJI]
Au!
Now, let us go.
[gasps]
[DORSHE]
Queen Hiling?
[HILING] What was that?
That sense of foreboding...
Foreboding, Your Majesty?
A sudden sensation
as if they're lost to me now.
Both Bojji...
...and Daida.
Please don't leave me alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないでよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaideyo
Since when did I start getting used to
いつから重たい荷物を持つ
itsukara omotai nimotsu o motsu
carrying a heavy burden day after day
日々に慣れてしまっていたんだろう
hibi ni nareteshimatteitan darou
Don't worry and set aside all your difficulties
難しいことは後回しでいいから
muzukashii koto wa atomawashide iikara
Night awaits me when I'm lonely
孤独なボクを夜が待つ
kodoku na boku o yoru ga matsu
Please don't make me feel lonely anymore
寂しい思いはもうボクにはさせないでよ
sabishii omoi wa mou boku ni wa sasenaideyo
Please don't seek solitude
思い出した夜を
omoidashita yoru o
when you remember that night
どうかひとりぼっちとは呼ばないで
douka hitori bocchito wa yobanaide
If you are weak
あなたが弱いのなら
anata ga yowai no nara
I'll show my weakness
ボクの弱さも見せるから
boku no yowasa mo miserukara
And if you pretend to be strong,
あなたが強がるのならば
anata ga tsuyogaru nonaraba
I'll gently embrace your weakness
キミの弱さをそっと抱きしめるよ
kimi no yowasa o sotto dakishimeruyo
I won't leave you alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaiyo