Domas.
I hereby appoint you to tutor my
son in the art of swordsmanship.
[gasps]
[BOSSE] I expect
great things, swordmaster.
[DOMAS grunts]
[DOMAS]
Prince Bojji.
I wish to teach you
all I know about the sword.
Learning it will demand a great
deal of effort from you,
but we will succeed!
To start, 1,000 push-ups.
[BOJJI grunting]
Though your first
attempts may falter,
you will grow stronger in time.
Maintain your stance.
Try and keep your back upright.
Ah!
[DOMAS sighs]
[DOMAS] I emulate
King Bosse in my swordsmanship.
My style meets all foes
with overwhelming force
and never retreats.
[BOJJI panting]
[DOMAS]
So what am I to do?
[BOJJI grunting]
[DOMAS] He is the one who's
suffering the most in this.
And yet...
[HILING]
That will be enough for today.
I thank you.
- [HILING] Domas.
- Yes?
[HILING] Does the boy have
any aptitude for the sword?
[DOMAS sighs]
It is still too soon to tell...
[HILING]
I see. Carry on, then.
[DOMAS]
Your Majesty.
[HILING]
Domas?
Your sign language
has greatly improved.
You may try it with Bojji.
[gasps] And do you believe
he would be pleased?
[HILING]
How should I know that?
[DOMAS]
Prince Bojji.
Has everything been going well?
[DOMAS grunts]
[DOMAS]
He understood!
[sniffs]
[grunting]
Au-au, ee-uh, ah, ah-uh.
Prince Bojji, you needn't
worry about a thing.
You will be fine
exactly as you are.
[DOMAS]
I swear to you...
...I will keep you safe.
Tears mingled with sweat
その涙が汗が滲んだ
sono namida ga ase ga nijinda
With your own unique beauty
誰とも違う美しさで
dare to mo chigau utsukushisa de
Smile for me
笑っておくれよ
waratte okureyo
Running out of breath, you're more wonderful than everyone else
息を切らした君は 誰より素敵さ
iki o kirashita kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Ranking of Kings
Almost melting into those listless days
気の抜けた炭酸みたいに
ki no nuketa tansan mitai ni
Feeling drained of energy like a flat soda
微かに気怠い日々に溶けた
kasuka ni kedarui hibi ni toketa
As a duckling, spread your wings,
家鴨の侭で翼を広げて
ahiru no mama de tsubasa o hirogete
dream of becoming a swan and soar through the sky
空を舞う白鳥の夢をみる
sora o mau shiratori no yume o miru
Put in your best effort rather than straying from the path
彷徨うくらいなら 一層味わい尽くしましょ
samayou kurai nara issou ajiwai tsukushimasho
For there's nothing fun about taking shortcuts, right?
近道ばかりじゃ 味気がないでしょ
chikamichi bakarija ajike ga naidesho
You took your time, choosing to take the hard road
道草を食って 泥濘み飲んで
michikusa o kutte nukarumi nonde
But you couldn't get there
でも辿り着けなくて
demo tadori tsukenakute
You keep chasing the sunset as many times as it takes
また何度だって 夕暮れを追いかけるの
mata nando datte yuugure o oikakeruno
Now run ahead
走れ遥か先へ
hashire haruka saki e
Your dirty shoes and footprints will definitely head towards the future
汚れた靴と足跡は 確かに未来へと
yogoreta kutsu to ashiato wa tashika ni mirai e to
Charging forward, running out of breath
今駆けてゆく 息を切らした
ima kaketeyuku iki o kirashita
You're more wonderful than everyone else
君は誰より素敵さ
kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Episode 4
His First Journey
[DORSHE]
Queen Hiling.
the judge from the Ranking
of Kings Committee
has just arrived.
[DORSHE] In the wake
of King Bosse's passing,
he is likely here to assess
the kingdom's ranking.
[MAGIC MIRROR] It is a king's
duty to act decisively
so that potential problems are
prevented before they occur.
There are those among your
subjects who would treat
the first prince's presence
as a means to sow discord
within the kingdom.
And if they did,
the ensuing unrest would
undoubtedly claim many lives.
Your duty as
the king is to avert
such catastrophes as these.
Therefore, the order to
assassinate Prince Bojji
was issued.
[DAIDA]
Yes. As you say.
[MAGIC MIRROR] With that done,
all that is left is to obtain
the strength of
King Bosse's body.
Will that really be necessary?
[MAGIC MIRROR] Yes, for though
you bear the vast potential
of youth, King Daida,
the power wielded
by King Bosse
was without peer.
[DAIDA]
Even so,
I wish to stake my reign
on my own power.
[JUDGE 4A] How many years
has it been now, Apeas?
From the committee, right?
Yes. It does take me back,
seeing you like this.
[panting]
[GOLEM 4A growls]
[JUDGE 4A] Had we judged
purely on strength,
King Bosse would have
placed first without a doubt.
On the subject...
I've heard a few
unsavory rumors.
It's been said that the king
who ranks highest will be
granted an item of his choosing
from the Divine Treasure Vault.
[JUDGE 4A]
Indeed.
[APEAS] And that each
successive king has chosen
the same treasure as the last,
before either disappearing
or succumbing to madness.
What is it that God grants them?
[JUDGE 4A]
That...
...I couldn't guess.
[HOKURO]
It's quite the prosperous town.
[DOMAS] Hmm. We should resupply
here before moving on.
Look after Prince Bojji.
Right.
Now―
[gasps]
Wait, Prince Bojji!
Prince Bojji?
[whimpers]
Oh, no...
[TROUPE 4A]
Ah! Please forgive me!
[TROUPE 4B]
Silence, you betrayer!
[TROUPE 4C]
Hold, villain! Now you face me!
[grunting]
Hang in there!
[applause]
[gasps]
Gold?! But how?!
Prince Bojji...
Where are you...?
[gasps]
[screams]
No! Prince Bojji!
[snoring]
[HOKURO groans]
[chuckles]
Stopping for a nap, are we?
Wait.
The bag...
Prince Bojji! Wake up!
Where's your bag?!
Do you know where it's gone?
Don't tell me...
Did somebody take it from you?!
You imbecile!
Your apology's not enough!
[HOKURO whines]
I'm so terribly sorry!
[BOJJI]
Ah, au, ah! Au!
Save your excuses!
Your mistakes
are our responsibility.
[DOMAS] Prince Bojji, the people
here work themselves ragged
and endure great hardships
to make enough money to survive.
You must refrain from tempting
them through displays of wealth.
[gasps]
[DOMAS] Please learn your lesson
from this lapse in judgment.
Au!
Now, did we have anything
of importance in that bag?
We did. Queen Hiling gave us a
letter to deliver to her family.
- That's an issue!
- I know!
You realize we― Gah.
[sighs] If there's nothing
to be done, then fine.
[HOKURO]
Uh?
Come. We should
get dinner ready.
[panting]
[JUDGE 4A]
Though it pains me to say this,
your initial placement will be
lower than your predecessor's.
As of right now,
I'd say around 90th place.
[DAIDA grunts]
[DOMAS] Are you prepared to
follow any order handed down
from your superiors?
What kind of orders
would they be giving me?
[DOMAS]
Whatever kind they see fit.
Will you obey them or not?
[HOKURO]
I couldn't say.
That shows a lack of resolve.
I will follow my orders.
Those we serve bear
pressures and responsibilities
beyond what you
or I could fathom.
It is not for us to question
the wisdom of their choices.
We are to enact their will
with no hesitation.
Yes, fair enough...
I hadn't considered that.
[DOMAS]
No. It's fine.
[HOKURO]
Prince Bojji...
What kind of pressures
and responsibilities
will you have to bear?
[HOKURO grunts]
[sighs]
Oh, thank you.
[DOMAS] The journey gets
more dangerous here.
We won't see
another town for a while.
[HOKURO]
Right.
[gasps]
Au!
[HOKURO]
Ah! Prince Bojji!
Wait, that bag...
Is it yours?
Everything is still in here.
But how could this happen?
[thudding]
[BEAST 4A growling]
[BOJJI gasps]
[thud]
[BOJJI]
Ah! Au!
[KAGE]
No matter what happens,
I've got your back
from now on, Bojji.
Ah-eh...
Halt, stranger!
You dare intrude on me?!
[BOJJI]
Au!
Ah, ah, ah-au!
Eh-eh-au-au!
Ya-ya-ya! Ya-ya-ya!
Yaah!
Uh, uh, uh!
Au...
[HUNTER 4A] A denizen
of the mundane world.
and what's more, you
seem unable to speak.
What brings you to this forest?
[BOJJI]
Ah―
[HUNTER 4A]
It compels you in its vastness.
Its mystery draws you in.
Its undeniable allure!
[BOAR 4A squeals]
[HUNTER 4A grunts]
[squealing]
Look there.
As we offer up
the flesh of this beast,
what we sacrifice is returned
to us many times over.
[laughs]
[HUNTER 4A]
Come and do as I do!
Ah.
[HUNTER 4A] This is the dance
of reconciliation.
Through this rite, we seek the
forgiveness of those whose lives
we take, and offer thanks for
the sustenance they give.
And so, their bodies are
returned to the forest anew
to be sacrificed once
more and sustain us.
[BOJJI panting]
[HUNTER 4A]
Eat.
It's good. Utterly delicious!
[grunts]
[squeals]
A mysterious thing,
and yet,
this is in the nature
of all living beings.
We sacrifice the lives of
others so we might feed
and thus sustain ourselves.
Hmm...
So tell me.
Would you let me offer
your life as my next sacrifice?
[gasps]
Ah...
[HOKURO]
Prince Bojji!
Look, there he is!
Oh, thank goodness!
You're not hurt.
We saw the fire and came here.
We both feared the worst.
[gasps]
What's happening?
Who's that?
[BOJJI grunting]
[HOKURO]
Ah?
[DOMAS]
Here, Prince Bojji.
Ah!
[DOMAS]
Keep alert!
Who goes there?!
Nobody's around,
but they were just here!
[DOMAS]
I can't sense anyone.
They've already left.
Who attacked, though?
Some highwaymen, most likely.
[FOX 4A whining]
[FOX KITS squeaking]
Must be a mother and her kits.
[snoring]
[DOMAS]
Bebin! I recognize your knives.
Don't hide! Show yourself!
[grunts]
[BOJJI sobbing]
[HOKURO] The knives must have
been laced with poison.
[sobbing continues]
Prince Bojji.
We should bury them.
There. Now they're
able to move on.
Surely, they'll be
happy in the next life.
Let us hope.
Do you know the town
we will be passing through?
No.
[DOMAS] There's a hole there
that leads to the underworld
called the Gates of Hell.
[HOKURO]
The Gates of Hell?
But the town seems
to be thriving.
It's always at peace, and the
monsters never encroach,
all thanks to its protectors.
The Order of the Underworld,
the greatest knights in history.
[DOMAS] Hokuro, find us
a place to stay the night.
Sir.
Prince Bojji.
I will escort you to see
the Gates of Hell directly.
[DOMAS] Every few minutes,
from this great chasm...
[BOJJI]
Ah!
...an enormous pillar
of flame is released,
like the fires of Hell itself
unleashed on Earth.
[DOMAS] Come forward and look,
Prince Bojji.
You will not see the bottom.
[BOJJI screams]
[HILING sighs]
[laughing]
[sobbing]
[DOMAS sobbing]
Prince Bojji... forgive me...
[sobbing]
Where am I? What the―
[HILING]
That is Pandora's Box.
You mustn't open it.
[DAIDA]
Mother?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
No.
You must open it,
for if you don't,
you shall never
reign as a true king.
Ah!
[DAIDA]
Mother!
[DAIDA] Mirror! It's too dark.
I can't see anything!
[whimpering]
[gasps]
Brother?
[HILING]
That is hope.
[MAGIC MIRROR] The only hope
you have of finding salvation.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[DAIDA]
Brother!
[gasps]
[HILING, MAGIC MIRROR] After
each fall, he rises once more.
And with his unfaltering
heart, wards off calamity.
[DAIDA whimpering]
[gasps]
A dream?
[growls]
Mirror!
Yes?
We mustn't delay.
I will claim Father's
strength immediately.
Please don't leave me alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないでよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaideyo
Since when did I start getting used to
いつから重たい荷物を持つ
itsukara omotai nimotsu o motsu
carrying a heavy burden day after day
日々に慣れてしまっていたんだろう
hibi ni nareteshimatteitan darou
Don't worry and set aside all your difficulties
難しいことは後回しでいいから
muzukashii koto wa atomawashide iikara
Night awaits me when I'm lonely
孤独なボクを夜が待つ
kodoku na boku o yoru ga matsu
Please don't make me feel lonely anymore
寂しい思いはもうボクにはさせないでよ
sabishii omoi wa mou boku ni wa sasenaideyo
Please don't seek solitude
思い出した夜を
omoidashita yoru o
when you remember that night
どうかひとりぼっちとは呼ばないで
douka hitori bocchito wa yobanaide
If you are weak
あなたが弱いのなら
anata ga yowai no nara
I'll show my weakness
ボクの弱さも見せるから
boku no yowasa mo miserukara
And if you pretend to be strong,
あなたが強がるのならば
anata ga tsuyogaru nonaraba
I'll gently embrace your weakness
キミの弱さをそっと抱きしめるよ
kimi no yowasa o sotto dakishimeruyo
I won't leave you alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaiyo