[BOJJI gasps]
[BOJJI grunts]
[gasps]
[BOJJI screams]
[whimpering]
[BOJJI]
Wah! Wa― Ah!
Ah...!
Ah!
[gasps]
Guess who's here?!
I just...
...I'm on your side, all right?
No matter what happens.
[gasps]
[whimpering]
Au... Ah...
Ah... Ah-eh...
Yeah, that's right, bud.
It's me, Kage.
[sobbing]
Ah... eh...
[KAGE grunts]
Don't cry, Bojji.
Let's be big boys, okay?
[BOJJI]
Ah. Au, au. [sobs]
Ah-ah...
[KAGE whimpers]
[BOTH sobbing]
Man, if you could
see your face right now!
Ah-ah, eh, ah.
[BOTH laugh]
Tears mingled with sweat
その涙が汗が滲んだ
sono namida ga ase ga nijinda
With your own unique beauty
誰とも違う美しさで
dare to mo chigau utsukushisa de
Smile for me
笑っておくれよ
waratte okureyo
Running out of breath, you're more wonderful than everyone else
息を切らした君は 誰より素敵さ
iki o kirashita kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Ranking of Kings
Almost melting into those listless days
気の抜けた炭酸みたいに
ki no nuketa tansan mitai ni
Feeling drained of energy like a flat soda
微かに気怠い日々に溶けた
kasuka ni kedarui hibi ni toketa
As a duckling, spread your wings,
家鴨の侭で翼を広げて
ahiru no mama de tsubasa o hirogete
dream of becoming a swan and soar through the sky
空を舞う白鳥の夢をみる
sora o mau shiratori no yume o miru
Put in your best effort rather than straying from the path
彷徨うくらいなら 一層味わい尽くしましょ
samayou kurai nara issou ajiwai tsukushimasho
For there's nothing fun about taking shortcuts, right?
近道ばかりじゃ 味気がないでしょ
chikamichi bakarija ajike ga naidesho
You took your time, choosing to take the hard road
道草を食って 泥濘み飲んで
michikusa o kutte nukarumi nonde
But you couldn't get there
でも辿り着けなくて
demo tadori tsukenakute
You keep chasing the sunset as many times as it takes
また何度だって 夕暮れを追いかけるの
mata nando datte yuugure o oikakeruno
Now run ahead
走れ遥か先へ
hashire haruka saki e
Your dirty shoes and footprints will definitely head towards the future
汚れた靴と足跡は 確かに未来へと
yogoreta kutsu to ashiato wa tashika ni mirai e to
Charging forward, running out of breath
今駆けてゆく 息を切らした
ima kaketeyuku iki o kirashita
You're more wonderful than everyone else
君は誰より素敵さ
kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Episode 5
Intertwining Plots
Guess what, bud?
I've been with you
every last step of the way!
[KAGE] When you fell off the
tower and bonked your head...
[KAGE] When that thief
ran off with your bag...
[KAGE] When you were about to
bite into that poisoned meat...
I was right there
to help you out each time!
[gasps]
As much as I hate to say this,
your life is still in
a lot of danger.
Back at the castle, that snake
guy asked me to escort you.
[KAGE]
He's tough to read, though.
Not sure what he's really up to.
But anyway, until we
could figure out who was
coming after you, we had to keep
all this a secret from you, too.
Gotta fool your friends
to fool your foes, you know.
Don't worry about it.
That's the way life
can be sometimes.
All right. Time to go.
Not the way we came―
We're heading deeper.
We're gonna be talking to
someone who can make you
the mightiest man there is!
Yeah, that's right!
Supposedly, he's way down
there in the underworld.
[DAIDA]
Enter.
[DOMAS]
You called, Your Majesty?
Yes, Domas. When you
voted for the next king,
why did you throw in
your lot with me?
[DOMAS gasps]
How could you know?
[DAIDA growls]
The weight of the crown is more
than Prince Bojji could bear.
Also... if I might be so bold,
you measure up better
to be the king―
[laughs]
Is that right?
You believed I would be
a better fit for the throne?
- [snarls]
- [gasps]
And did you think nothing
of your duty to your pupil,
you coward?!
You betrayed my brother
in handing me the crown
and brought disgrace
upon my court!
[DOMAS]
I've no defense, Your Majesty.
[DAIDA] Tch. On that day,
after I sparred with you,
I was sure you were
someone I could trust.
Truly, I was.
Yet you've defied
my best expectations.
[DAIDA]
Domas...
You are an extraordinarily
capable man,
and I long dreamed you
would serve as my right hand
in leading this kingdom.
[gasps]
It seems that will stay a dream.
You're not who
I thought you were.
[DOMAS]
King Daida, how can I fix this?
[DAIDA] For the sake of
this kingdom and its people,
I have come to a decision,
but what must be done next
is something I could
only ask of a servant
whom I can trust absolutely.
[DOMAS]
Please! You can trust me!
I should be proud.
I've done my duty
to king and country.
This pain in my heart must be
punishment for the weakness
of my resolve.
Surely, that's it.
There's nothing else
it could be.
[DOMAS chuckling]
[KAGE]
This is a deep hole.
[grunting]
We're still not to the bottom.
Oh! That's right!
Bleh.
[KAGE]
Here.
It's just a little cloth crown,
but you'll look way
more like yourself.
[gasps]
Au-ah.
Sure.
- [BOJJI] Hmph!
- Yeah! There's the real Bojji!
Your whole get-up feels a little
generic without it, honestly.
[BOJJI]
Hmm!
[BOTH grunt]
[KAGE]
Egad!
A human skull...
What the heck could've
happened down here?
[sniffing]
Hey, what's the matter?
[BOJJI]
Au, ah, au.
You smell something? Like what?
[BOJJI sniffing]
Huh?
Look out, gas!
This is where those pillars
of fire come from.
Run, Bojji!
[KAGE grunting]
[BOJJI grunts]
[groans]
[sighs]
[horse shoes clopping]
[DAIDA] I never realized
how deep this passage went.
Mirror. What are you, really?
[MAGIC MIRROR] A sworn ally
who shared the joys and sorrows
of your father.
A satisfactory answer, yes?
[DAIDA]
Hmm...
Ah...
[gulps]
[grunts]
Who are you two?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
They are both loyal servants
of the late King Bosse.
And they shall aid you
in assuming his power.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Please, enter.
[DAIDA grunts]
[gasps]
[MAGIC MIRROR] Here,
you will find many creatures
all entombed in ice.
Huh...
[DAIDA]
What is this place?
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[DAIDA]
Father!
[MAGIC MIRROR] He was
brought here after his death,
to be preserved,
in preparation for this moment.
How did you...?
[metal creaking]
Tell me what's happening, now!
[gears grinding]
[DAIDA whimpering]
[grinding continues]
[DAIDA retches]
You monsters!
How could you do that?!
[MAGIC MIRROR] This is where
it begins, King Daida.
[APEAS grunting]
[GRIFFIN 5A screeches]
[MAGIC MIRROR] In that ball,
the marrow of King Bosse's bones
is being mixed with a secret
potion that I provided.
What's this madness?
[MAGIC MIRROR] The lenses are
focusing the light on the ball,
heating it and
changing its contents.
[DAIDA]
It's glowing like the sun.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
It hatches.
[gasps]
[PHOENIX 5A roars]
[DAIDA grunts]
This is disgusting...
[PHOENIX 5A screeches]
[DAIDA gasps]
[PHOENIX 5A roars]
[PHOENIX 5A screeches]
[DAIDA gasps]
[whimpering]
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Its blood is holy.
[DAIDA whimpers]
[MAGIC MIRROR] Its body has
been burned, and from its ashes,
the Jewel of Resurrection
can now be retrieved.
[MAGIC MIRROR] This ingredient
will complete the elixir.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Now. Drink, King Daida.
You would have me drink this?
[MAGIC MIRROR] Once you do,
you will gain the almighty power
of King Bosse.
A power unrivaled in this world.
[DAIDA grunts]
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Now, drink.
[MAGIC MIRROR chuckles]
I won't.
How could I trust
this vile concoction?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
But King Daida, does that mean
you don't trust me?
I can't do what you're asking.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Have you forgotten your drop
in the ranking?
How could I forget?!
That's exactly the reason
I have to try harder,
for as long as it takes!
[MAGIC MIRROR] Venturing into
this world, you'll find that
it refuses to slow its workings
to accommodate your pace.
[DAIDA]
I realize that.
But even so...
I don't know why,
I-I just can't do this!
[MAGIC MIRROR] Indeed,
your hesitation is only natural,
but what you stand to
gain by drinking that elixir
is power beyond imagining.
Perhaps you should
drink it yourself, Mirror!
Or what about the two
of you?! Take it!
[MAGIC MIRROR] It will have no
effect unless drunk by one
bearing the blood of King Bosse.
Do please try and
imagine it, King Daida.
Assuming the power of
King Bosse as your own,
and using it to soar
through the Ranking of Kings.
Imagine reigning
over all the world.
[DAIDA]
And if I drink this, will I...?
[DAIDA panting]
Prince Daida, no endeavor
worth your while
will offer an easy path.
At times, your struggles
will define you.
Keep that in mind, and don't be
deceived by those around you,
or especially yourself.
[DAIDA]
I won't drink it.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
King Daida―
That's enough, Mirror!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Then so be it.
What's the meaning of this?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
It is for your own sake.
[DAIDA grunts]
[grunting]
[DAIDA]
Do not trifle with me.
Mirror...
It may be true that you're
acting in my interest,
but no. I will take
the top rank by my own power!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Stop. Y-You can't!
Ah, Master Domas!
There you are!
[HOKURO] Um. Wait.
But where is Prince Bojji?
Prince Bojji is
no longer with us.
Uh. Has he gone somewhere, then?
Master Domas? Where is he?
He's not in this world anymore!
[HOKURO]
Guh― You can't mean he―
[fire booming]
[gasps]
[HOKURO]
Ah... Ah?
Say it isn't so...
Surely, you could never...
[DESHA] Hmm. Then they
survived the cursed gas?
[DESHA]
I see.
They each came bearing
a curse already.
Naturally, the gas
wouldn't kill them.
One is a giant
stripped of his power.
The other, a shadow clan
member in an altered form,
marked by divine disfavor.
Though indeed, the little crown
is undoubtedly the work
of a master craftsman!
[laughs]
You've done well.
This will suitably pass my time.
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Sire.
[DESHA]
Heh.
Awaken!
- Ah!
- [KAGE] Yah!
[BOTH gasp]
[DESHA] Hmph. I see.
The son of Bosse has come here.
[HOKURO]
Master Domas!
The goal of this excursion
was to eliminate Prince Bojji.
[gasps]
And you were willing to
accept that mission...?
Is he really dead?
- [DOMAS] Yes.
- [growls]
[DOMAS]
By my hand.
You dare...?
I have to.
I've failed my duty
to protect Prince Bojji!
You're a fool!
Who's the fool?!
Yaah!
[BOTH groaning]
[DOMAS]
Quit while you can!
[HOKURO grunts, groans]
[HOKURO grunting]
[HOKURO]
All of this...
The whole journey...
What have I been doing?!
[snarls]
[huffing]
[screams]
[splortch]
Now follow that strike
through and sever my hand!
[HOKURO snarls]
[yells]
Gah!
[DOMAS huffing]
Please don't leave me alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないでよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaideyo
Since when did I start getting used to
いつから重たい荷物を持つ
itsukara omotai nimotsu o motsu
carrying a heavy burden day after day
日々に慣れてしまっていたんだろう
hibi ni nareteshimatteitan darou
Don't worry and set aside all your difficulties
難しいことは後回しでいいから
muzukashii koto wa atomawashide iikara
Night awaits me when I'm lonely
孤独なボクを夜が待つ
kodoku na boku o yoru ga matsu
Please don't make me feel lonely anymore
寂しい思いはもうボクにはさせないでよ
sabishii omoi wa mou boku ni wa sasenaideyo
Please don't seek solitude
思い出した夜を
omoidashita yoru o
when you remember that night
どうかひとりぼっちとは呼ばないで
douka hitori bocchito wa yobanaide
If you are weak
あなたが弱いのなら
anata ga yowai no nara
I'll show my weakness
ボクの弱さも見せるから
boku no yowasa mo miserukara
And if you pretend to be strong,
あなたが強がるのならば
anata ga tsuyogaru nonaraba
I'll gently embrace your weakness
キミの弱さをそっと抱きしめるよ
kimi no yowasa o sotto dakishimeruyo
I won't leave you alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaiyo