My only wish is to become
the strongest man in the world.
Will you grant me
what I desire, o demon?
[murmuring]
[MIRANJO] "I could, although
it would come at the cost
of your life."
That's no matter. Living a long
life was never my intention.
[murmuring]
[MIRANJO] "However, though
I can give this power to you.
I cannot simply
conjure it into being."
"If I am to grant you strength,
it must be taken from one
who bears your blood."
That won't work.
I haven't got any living kin.
[murmurs]
He says you need
but sire a child.
Huh. I accept.
Demon! Seal the pact
and grant me my wish!
[laughs]
Tears mingled with sweat
その涙が汗が滲んだ
sono namida ga ase ga nijinda
With your own unique beauty
誰とも違う美しさで
dare to mo chigau utsukushisa de
Smile for me
笑っておくれよ
waratte okureyo
Running out of breath, you're more wonderful than everyone else
息を切らした君は 誰より素敵さ
iki o kirashita kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Ranking of Kings
Almost melting into those listless days
気の抜けた炭酸みたいに
ki no nuketa tansan mitai ni
Feeling drained of energy like a flat soda
微かに気怠い日々に溶けた
kasuka ni kedarui hibi ni toketa
As a duckling, spread your wings,
家鴨の侭で翼を広げて
ahiru no mama de tsubasa o hirogete
dream of becoming a swan and soar through the sky
空を舞う白鳥の夢をみる
sora o mau shiratori no yume o miru
Put in your best effort rather than straying from the path
彷徨うくらいなら 一層味わい尽くしましょ
samayou kurai nara issou ajiwai tsukushimasho
For there's nothing fun about taking shortcuts, right?
近道ばかりじゃ 味気がないでしょ
chikamichi bakarija ajike ga naidesho
You took your time, choosing to take the hard road
道草を食って 泥濘み飲んで
michikusa o kutte nukarumi nonde
But you couldn't get there
でも辿り着けなくて
demo tadori tsukenakute
You keep chasing the sunset as many times as it takes
また何度だって 夕暮れを追いかけるの
mata nando datte yuugure o oikakeruno
Now run ahead
走れ遥か先へ
hashire haruka saki e
Your dirty shoes and footprints will definitely head towards the future
汚れた靴と足跡は 確かに未来へと
yogoreta kutsu to ashiato wa tashika ni mirai e to
Charging forward, running out of breath
今駆けてゆく 息を切らした
ima kaketeyuku iki o kirashita
You're more wonderful than everyone else
君は誰より素敵さ
kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Episode 8
The Sacrifice of Dreams
[GIANT MONSTER 8A groaning]
[panting]
[thudding]
[BOSSE] You are the strongest
woman in the world, are you not?
My name is Bosse.
I need to speak with you.
What about?
Did you come here for a fight?
- [BOSSE] No.
- [SHIINA] Hmm?
I want you to marry me
and bear me a child.
Huh?!
You speak nonsense!
I live only in pursuit
of strength!
[BOSSE] My dream is to become
the strongest man in the world,
and I will not rest until
I've made it come true!
[SHIINA grunts]
Then show me.
[BOSSE]
So be it.
[BOTH grunt]
[SHIINA, BOSSE panting]
You're quite strong.
Just as a man should be.
Huh?
[laughs]
Straightforward, as well!
[sighs] Why did I feel so
compelled to become stronger?
Could it be that the men around
simply weren't strong enough?
[SHIINA]
Hmm? No, it wasn't that.
Ahem. Right. Pardon.
[SHIINA laughs]
[BOSSE, SHIINA laughing]
[panting]
[OGRE 8A growls]
[BOSSE groans]
My child... is born.
[BOSSE growls]
[bellows]
[OGRES screaming]
[VILLAGER 8A]
She just gave birth!
Huh?
[chuckles]
You've been spilling
blood, haven't you?
And as you were out ending
lives, a new one was born.
Sorry.
[SHIINA]
Look; he's a boy.
But a rather small one for the
child of two giants, isn't he?
[BOSSE gasps]
[MIRANJO]
"If I am to grant you strength,
it must be taken from one
who bears your blood."
[SHIINA]
Hmm. Even so, he's very cute.
[BOJJI babbles]
[BOSSE huffing]
[BOSSE snarls]
[VILLAGERS gasping]
This place will mark
the end of my long journey.
Hear me! I will make this land
the seat of my kingdom!
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[BOSSE] My son... shall live
a life unconstrained by want.
I will make that my only goal.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
King Bosse.
Do you wish to know who is the
strongest person in the world
as of this moment?
You're saying it isn't me?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
You must recite the incantation.
[DAIDA sighs]
Mirror, Mirror, hear my call.
Who is the strongest
of them all?
[MAGIC MIRROR] This person
is the strongest alive.
[gasps]
[laughs]
[MAGIC MIRROR] So, then,
are you feeling reassured?
An interesting turn of events.
Very interesting.
[MAGIC MIRROR] King Bosse... The
time has come to kill Hiling.
Will you give your blessing?
As promised, so long ago.
[HILING whimpers]
Then, Bojji...
He's really...
[HOKURO whimpering]
I had orders and
I couldn't defy them.
It wasn't my place.
- Please, wait.
- [gasps]
Listen to what
I have to say first.
When I chose to let you live,
I forfeited my place
at the castle.
If I return,
my life could be at risk.
And I'm not ready to give it up
yet, so I won't be going back.
[growls] I can't believe
what a coward you are!
Hokuro, what do you expect
them to do when you return?
That doesn't matter.
It's my duty to report this.
Your report would find
its way to the person
who gave the order.
The king himself.
[gasps]
Queen Hiling knows
nothing of this,
and King Daida
is her own beloved child.
What will she do when you tell
her he had his brother killed?
I'll leave out your
explanations and only tell her
what I saw for myself!
Will you?
Clearly, I've done neither of us
any favors by leaving you alive.
[HOKURO]
Spare me your pity.
[growls]
Stop trying to play the hero!
You did leave me alive,
which means I'm obliged
to return to the castle...
...and inform the queen!
Because she loved Prince Bojji!
And if his soul can't
seek comfort from those
who loved him...
...after everything
he went through...
...then all his suffering
was for nothing!
[DOMAS growls]
- [HOKURO groans]
- [DOMAS] Damn it.
Damn it! You're a fool!
[coughing]
Go and die the finest
death you can.
[HOKURO growls]
[DOMAS laughs]
[HOKURO snarls]
[sobs]
[HILING]
Limb from limb...
[gasps]
You'll be torn...
limb from limb!
[MONSTER 8A growls]
These monsters...
You plan to turn them
against Hiling?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Indeed.
Are they strong?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Of course.
Forward, Apeas.
[gasps]
[APEAS grunts]
[MONSTER 8B growling]
[APEAS]
The first one was drawing me in?
[APEAS groans]
[APEAS grunts]
[MONSTER 8B growls]
[APEAS]
Hmph.
I got sloppy.
[MAGIC MIRROR chuckles]
Stand down, Apeas.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
King Bosse!
[gasps]
[MONSTERS growling]
What's the matter?
[DAIDA]
Hmph.
[MONSTERS growling]
[DAIDA]
Forgive me, Miranjo.
My blood hasn't raced
like that in a while.
Your plan to assassinate Hiling.
- [MAGIC MIRROR] Yes?
- I approve.
Your Majesty...
[MAGIC MIRROR chuckles]
[HILING growls]
[DOMAS] Dorshe is the only
one who poses a threat.
[DOMAS] How did I trick myself
into coming back here?
But you did leave me alive,
which means I'm obliged
to return to the castle
and inform the queen!
Heh.
Pride just weighs you down
in the end, eh, Hokuro?
[SOLDIER 8A]
Ready!
[HOKURO]
Prince Bojji...
Mom...
I'm coming!
[HILING growling]
- [SOLDIERS yelling]
- [SOLDIER 8A] What was that?!
[gasps]
Queen Hiling.
Do not leave my side.
[grunting, yelling]
- [DOMAS] Hokuro!
- [gasps]
[yelling]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[DORSHE gasps]
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[HOKURO grunts]
[DOMAS snarls]
[gasping]
[DOMAS gasps]
Who goes there?
Daida?
[DOMAS]
King Daida?
Wait... No.
It's not...
Th-This is...
What happened here?
[HOKURO gulps]
[DOMAS grunts]
[DORSHE]
He parried! That technique...
You're Domas.
[gasps]
[DOMAS]
No!
[DOMAS grunts]
[groans]
- [SOLDIER 8A] Wait. Is that...?
- [SOLDIER 8B] Impossible!
- [SOLDIER 8C] It's him!
- [SOLDIER 8D] Master Domas!
What is this?!
[chuckles]
Hokuro. Apologies.
Master, you came...
[growls]
Go, Dorshe!
I want Domas's head!
Your Majesty?!
Go, take his head! Right now!
That's enough!
Bojji is safe!
He is not dead!
[gasping]
[SOLDIER 8D]
But then, what's happening...?
[DAIDA]
Mirror, Mirror, hear my call.
Who is the strongest
of them all?
[MAGIC MIRROR] This person
is the strongest alive.
[gasps]
[DAIDA]
Hmm.
[BOTH chuckling]
[hissing]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[grunting, groaning]
[hissing, growling]
[BEBIN grunts]
[BEBIN groaning]
[BOSSE]
Hmph.
Bebin, from this day forward,
you shall serve with
the royal elite forces.
[gasps]
I expect great things...
snake charmer.
- Heh.
- [gasps]
[BEBIN grunts]
I owe you one.
You are not in my debt.
You have given me far more
than could ever be repaid
through a gesture such
as this, Master Bebin.
[BEBIN]
Hmm.
[sighs]
[SOLDIER 8F]
What is going on here?
[DAIDA chuckles]
Bojji's journeyed to the
underworld for his training!
He grows stronger
as we speak!
[gasps]
- [HILING sighs]
- [DORSHE gasps]
He's really... still alive?
[DAIDA]
He is, indeed.
And therefore,
your life is spared.
You are hereby relieved
of duty and banished
from the castle
with these words.
[inaudible]
[gasps]
[DAIDA]
Now begone.
[DOMAS grunts]
Yes, sire.
We're leaving now, Hokuro.
[HOKURO grunts]
Sir!
[HOKURO]
Master Domas!
Is it true? Could Prince
Bojji really still be alive
like King Daida was saying?
[DOMAS]
It could be.
I didn't follow him into the pit
to confirm he was dead.
Perhaps Bebin's
network informed the king.
What do you think?
I'm sure... the prince
must have made it!
[DOMAS]
Right. Of course.
He's alive.
He...
[sobs]
He must be...
Uh, Master Domas?
[DOMAS sniffles]
One more thing.
That was not King Daida,
but King Bosse.
What?!
[DOMAS]
I don't fully understand,
but King Bosse has returned.
He lives on within
the body of Daida.
[HOKURO]
Impossible...
But where is King Daida, then?
[DOMAS] I couldn't even
begin to answer that.
Listen.
[HOKURO]
Sir!
[DOMAS] I need to find a way
to use my right arm again.
Then... I'll teach
you swordsmanship.
[gasps]
[DOMAS] Where we're going,
you'll need it to stay alive.
Where will we be going?
[DOMAS] Deep beneath the castle,
to a gateway that opens
into the underworld.
[HOKURO]
The underworld...?
[DOMAS] A fell place that draws
monsters to it like a beacon.
We're going to close it off.
Why wait until now
to deal with that?
[DOMAS]
I don't know.
I was only told to destroy it.
There has to be more to this.
[HOKURO] I can't forgive
what you did to Prince Bojji,
and I doubt I ever will.
But even if I'd been there,
I understand that I
couldn't have saved him...
...because I'm too soft.
That's why I have
to become stronger.
I look forward
to learning from you!
[DOMAS]
You've helped me recognize
something, too, Hokuro.
[HOKURO gasps]
I had forgotten just how
valuable innocence can be.
Prince Bojji's alive!
Though I could
hardly bear to face him.
No--that's not
important right now.
We've got orders!
Focus on nothing
but the task at hand!
[HOKURO]
Right!
[DOMAS bellows]
[HOKURO bellows]
[KAGE]
Did itty bitty Bojji actually...
[BOJJI]
Ay!
[KAGE] No way. Bojji couldn't
even budge a hammer like that,
let alone swing it.
But what is he using?
- [DESPA] Kage.
- [KAGE] Yah!
Don't sneak up on me like that!
Oh, hey, Bojji's here with you.
[BOJJI]
Mm!
What's up?
The long-awaited day
has finally come.
What day?
Prince Bojji has fully
mastered the Despa arts.
[KAGE]
"Fully mastered"?
Au!
[HILING]
King Daida.
Have you... changed, somehow?
You still can't tell who I am?
Huh?
Dorshe.
[DORSHE]
Sire?
En garde.
[DORSHE groans]
[gasps]
[DORSHE grunts]
Wait. What did you just do?
[laughs] As I would expect
from the Big Four's strongest.
[yelps]
[inaudible]
[gasps]
[MAGIC MIRROR] Apeas, do you
have any idea what King Bosse
might be whispering to them?
A good question.
I can't say.
- [DAIDA] Hiling.
- [gasps]
Don't be fooled. Your eyes
tell you I am your son, Daida,
but in truth, I am Bosse.
Where is this place?
[DAIDA whimpering]
Mirror! Where are you, Mirror?!
[DAIDA]
In the chamber...
...Apeas knocked me out
with a surprise blow.
Did they toss me
into a cell somewhere?
[DAIDA]
No...
Something is strange here.
Please don't leave me alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないでよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaideyo
Since when did I start getting used to
いつから重たい荷物を持つ
itsukara omotai nimotsu o motsu
carrying a heavy burden day after day
日々に慣れてしまっていたんだろう
hibi ni nareteshimatteitan darou
Don't worry and set aside all your difficulties
難しいことは後回しでいいから
muzukashii koto wa atomawashide iikara
Night awaits me when I'm lonely
孤独なボクを夜が待つ
kodoku na boku o yoru ga matsu
Please don't make me feel lonely anymore
寂しい思いはもうボクにはさせないでよ
sabishii omoi wa mou boku ni wa sasenaideyo
Please don't seek solitude
思い出した夜を
omoidashita yoru o
when you remember that night
どうかひとりぼっちとは呼ばないで
douka hitori bocchito wa yobanaide
If you are weak
あなたが弱いのなら
anata ga yowai no nara
I'll show my weakness
ボクの弱さも見せるから
boku no yowasa mo miserukara
And if you pretend to be strong,
あなたが強がるのならば
anata ga tsuyogaru nonaraba
I'll gently embrace your weakness
キミの弱さをそっと抱きしめるよ
kimi no yowasa o sotto dakishimeruyo
I won't leave you alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaiyo