[DAIDA] Hiling. Your eyes
fooled you into believing
I am your son, Daida,
but in truth, I am Bosse.
Wha... How...?
Daida, what is this?
[groaning]
[gasps]
[DAIDA grunting]
[snarls]
[gasping]
[DORSHE gasps]
[DAIDA groaning]
[panting]
[gasps]
I am who I say I am.
But...
But wouldn't that mean...
If you really are King Bosse,
then where is Daida?
Do you know what's
become of our son?
I don't.
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[DORSHE]
Queen Hiling!
Tears mingled with sweat
その涙が汗が滲んだ
sono namida ga ase ga nijinda
With your own unique beauty
誰とも違う美しさで
dare to mo chigau utsukushisa de
Smile for me
笑っておくれよ
waratte okureyo
Running out of breath, you're more wonderful than everyone else
息を切らした君は 誰より素敵さ
iki o kirashita kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Ranking of Kings
Almost melting into those listless days
気の抜けた炭酸みたいに
ki no nuketa tansan mitai ni
Feeling drained of energy like a flat soda
微かに気怠い日々に溶けた
kasuka ni kedarui hibi ni toketa
As a duckling, spread your wings,
家鴨の侭で翼を広げて
ahiru no mama de tsubasa o hirogete
dream of becoming a swan and soar through the sky
空を舞う白鳥の夢をみる
sora o mau shiratori no yume o miru
Put in your best effort rather than straying from the path
彷徨うくらいなら 一層味わい尽くしましょ
samayou kurai nara issou ajiwai tsukushimasho
For there's nothing fun about taking shortcuts, right?
近道ばかりじゃ 味気がないでしょ
chikamichi bakarija ajike ga naidesho
You took your time, choosing to take the hard road
道草を食って 泥濘み飲んで
michikusa o kutte nukarumi nonde
But you couldn't get there
でも辿り着けなくて
demo tadori tsukenakute
You keep chasing the sunset as many times as it takes
また何度だって 夕暮れを追いかけるの
mata nando datte yuugure o oikakeruno
Now run ahead
走れ遥か先へ
hashire haruka saki e
Your dirty shoes and footprints will definitely head towards the future
汚れた靴と足跡は 確かに未来へと
yogoreta kutsu to ashiato wa tashika ni mirai e to
Charging forward, running out of breath
今駆けてゆく 息を切らした
ima kaketeyuku iki o kirashita
You're more wonderful than everyone else
君は誰より素敵さ
kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Episode 9
The Queen and the Shield
[HILING]
Daida...
[groaning]
Where have you gone?
[DORSHE]
Hmm?
[HILING]
Daida...
The queen mustn't leave her
chambers under any circumstance.
Do you understand?
[growling]
[DORSHE]
King Bosse.
[BOSSE]
Dorshe?
You've stripped my position
as Spear of the King
and reassigned me as
the new queen's personal guard.
But why?
What is it that threatens her?
Your kingdom is at peace,
and the queen lives here
at its very heart.
Your Majesty!
For now, just follow your
orders and stay with the queen.
If in time, you find that
protecting her is not
a worthwhile use
of your talents,
then we'll revisit this.
[DORSHE sighs]
[DORSHE] I must have lost
the king's trust.
He has no confidence in me.
[HILING]
My bodyguard? You?
Yes.
Well, you're needlessly large
and distressingly unkempt.
Hmph!
[HILING] But the king has
charged you with guarding me,
and guard me you shall.
I would ask only that
you keep your distance.
But duty compels me to stay
by your side, Your Majesty.
What duty could
compel you to defy me?!
I am your queen!
Ah. Forgive me, Your Majesty!
Look over there.
[gasps]
This has to do with the prince?
Yes, it does.
I will be that boy's mother.
But first, I need him
to open up to me,
and that's proven
difficult thus far.
I can hardly imagine having you
there towering over us both
would put him more at ease.
[DORSHE]
Uh...
- [BOJJI] Ah?
- Oh, Prince.
I have a treat here for you!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Now, hold on!
Don't you want some
of this cake, Prince?
[panting]
Delicious cake...
There's... cake...
[groans]
[panting]
I swear. How can
he run so quickly?
Ah?
Ah!
Ah.
[MAID 3C]
To greet him, you'd say,
"How are you?" Like this.
[HILING]
Am I doing it right?
Yes! Exactly like that!
- Ah?
- Oh, Prince!
How are you? Doing well?
Prince, hold on!
[growls]
Why didn't it work?!
I did as you said!
[whines]
Forgive me, Your Majesty!
[sobbing]
Sorry... Surely,
I just need to practice.
Forgive me.
Please, continue teaching me.
[MAID 3C sobs]
Yes, Your Majesty...
[DORSHE]
She's unexpectedly awkward.
Do you believe I've lost trust
in you and relegated you
to a lesser post?
[DORSHE]
Uh?
You're ruled by your emotions.
To stand at the king's side,
you must be ready to carry out
his orders without regard for
your own feelings, like Apeas.
[BOSSE]
Hmm. Now, then.
Do you believe that Hiling
is worth protecting?
[SORII] It seems cruel
to even ask such a thing
about the queen.
[BOSSE]
What say you, Dorshe?
[DORSHE] Though I understand, my
duty is not to my own beliefs.
Yes, she is.
[BOSSE]
Hmm?
As are all people.
[BOSSE] Hmm. He is quite
suited for the task.
Quite.
There you are, my queen!
It's all right.
This person is my bodyguard.
He keeps us safe.
Look at him.
[DORSHE grunts]
Au...
You're all right.
He just needs some time
to get used to you.
Now quit moping!
I know what I'm doing,
so chin up!
Okay! Now, let's run!
[laughs]
[BOJJI giggles]
[gasps]
[grunting]
Here he comes!
Don't slow down!
[BOTH laughing]
[DORSHE huffing]
See that?
He came after us.
Au! Au! Au!
[panting]
Yes, Your Majesty?
I expected you to be
far quicker on your feet.
Can I really trust you
to protect me?
[DORSHE]
You can.
I won't allow you
to come to any harm.
[DORSHE groans]
[growling]
[DORSHE grunts, growls]
[DORSHE groans]
Gaugh!
[DORSHE grunts]
[gasps]
Yaugh!
[DORSHE chuckles]
Hmph!
[DORSHE]
No!
[snarls]
[gasps, grunts]
[groans]
[DORSHE] I can't just
hold them off forever.
I need to end this.
[snarls]
Here!
[MAGIC MIRROR] These creatures
are nimble and capable of
inflicting grievous
wounds with ease.
In packs, they can even
overcome the mighty Gigantes.
[MAGIC MIRROR chuckles]
[MAGIC MIRROR]
"Witch's Enchantment."
In terms of raw power,
those monsters are not
a match for Dorshe.
But if he should remove
his armor, their claws and fangs
will make short work of him.
Dorshe will fail
to protect Hiling.
[DORSHE growls]
[DORSHE bellows]
[DORSHE roars]
[gasps]
[exhales]
[screams]
[huffing]
There's going to be an attempt
on the life of Hiling.
One which I won't move to stop.
[gasps]
[DAIDA] Will you stay
at her side or will you
choose to follow me?
[DORSHE] You appointed me as her
bodyguard, but now, you're―
King Bosse, what could
be your real goal?
[growls]
[retches]
[bellows]
[growling]
[crack]
[groans]
[snarls]
[DORSHE panting]
Can't... drop my... guard...
Have to protect Hiling...
[MAGIC MIRROR]
But how?!
What is it?
[MAGIC MIRROR] I can
no longer sense the monsters.
The assassination has failed.
I see.
[MAGIC MIRROR gasps]
[DAIDA sighs]
Miranjo.
Let us not waste this rare
moment we've been granted.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
King Bosse...
[MIRANJO]
Your Majesty...
My joy is more than
I can put in words.
At last...
At long last!
[MAGIC MIRROR panting]
My magic's given out.
[panting]
I'm powerless.
That couldn't be less true.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
King Bosse...
I must go to
the underworld once again.
I shall return to you with
more monsters to serve you.
Tell me. What could drive you
to such lengths, Miranjo?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Your Majesty...
Forgive me.
I truly do wish to give you
that which you desire.
Perhaps I'm distorted
to the core.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
I surely am...
...something twisted--and ugly.
You're not, Miranjo.
You're as perfect and pure
as anything in this world.
[MAGIC MIRROR chuckles weakly]
[sobbing]
It's all right.
You are not alone.
I am right here.
[DORSHE]
Am I... dead?
[HILING]
You most certainly are not.
As if I'd let you die.
Ah!
Forgive me, Queen Hiling!
I will repay this kindness!
That's quite enough.
It's only thanks to you
that I'm alive.
I'm all done.
[HILING]
Thank you.
[HILING] Now, it's my turn
to fight against the king.
[gasps]
And I will win Daida back.
[DAIDA whimpering]
[DAIDA]
Nothing...
I walk and I walk...
...and go nowhere!
[grunting]
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[screams]
[DAIDA] Am I going to spend
the rest of my existence
stumbling aimlessly through
this endless nothingness?
No... No. No!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Once more, to the underworld!
I shall bring the mightiest
under my control
and march onward to a new age
at King Bosse's side!
Your Majesty.
Please don't be rash!
We can't say for certain that
this attack was orchestrated
by King Bosse!
Queen Hiling!
I couldn't be more certain
that he's involved somehow.
I will hear his
explanation for myself!
Queen Hiling has come.
[HILING grunts]
Answer me. What's driven
you to do all this?!
Something utterly trivial.
And for this trivial matter,
you were willing to deceive us?!
And you would even steal
Daida's body from him?!
Daida! Our own son!
As you say, it's all my doing.
How can you sound so calm
after what you've done?!
You speak as if
you weren't part of it!
[growls]
Give Daida back this instant!
You were dead, and you
should've stayed dead!
[sobs]
You can still make
things right, so please...
Show me you haven't
sunk this low!
[sobs]
As the king--no, as his father―
truly, have you no shame?
Where is he?!
What did you do to our son?!
[gasps] I can hear somebody's
voice calling out
through the void. Is that...?
Mother! Where are you?!
[gasps]
Is something wrong?
I'm sure...
...I just heard...
[DAIDA panting]
I'm here, Mother!
Daida!
Huh?
[HILING]
Daida! Where are you?!
- Daida?!
- [DAIDA panting] I'm here!
Daida! Daida!
Mother!
Daida!
[panting]
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
[DAIDA grunts]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[DAIDA wailing]
[sobbing]
Mother...
Please!
Mother...!
[gasps]
Daida! That's where you are!
- [HILING grunts]
- [gasps]
I'm here! Daida.
I can hear your voice!
[gasps]
It's you!
Ah! Thank goodness you're safe!
It'll be okay. Your mother
will bring you back,
whatever it takes!
Come, Dorshe!
Daida is right here!
He's crying out for help!
[DORSHE]
U-Uh...
Dorshe! Go save Daida!
What are you waiting for?!
He's here with us!
Can't you hear his voice?!
No, Queen Hiling.
Your Majesty's voice
is the only one I hear.
[HILING gasps]
[snarls]
Ah! Queen Hiling!
[HILING]
Dah! Hrgh...!
- [DORSHE grunts]
- Oh!
Let go of me!
I have to save my son!
You would be taking a dagger
to his own body!
[gasps]
[sobbing]
Dorshe!
[grunts, groans]
I beg your forgiveness,
Your Majesty...
Listen, Dorshe.
I don't expect another attack
against Hiling for a while,
but she won't survive the next
one when it comes.
[gasps]
Get her out of the country
if you want her to live,
and then...
bide your time there.
[DORSHE]
What will happen if we wait?
At this point, I don't know
much more than the rest of you.
Now go!
Aye.
I can't hear Mother anymore...
[gasps]
It couldn't be...
No... It can't be!
No! No!
[sobs]
Mother!
[wailing]
Please help me.
Please help me...
[growls]
She did this...
It's all her fault!
I will destroy you.
You hear me?!
I swear it, Mirror!
I'll kill you!
But... how do I get out of here?
[sniffles]
[DAIDA]
Everything is dark...
I hear only silence,
and the crushing waves
of anxiety rolling in...
[BOJJI sobbing]
[DAIDA] Could this be what
Brother's world is like?
Please don't leave me alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないでよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaideyo
Since when did I start getting used to
いつから重たい荷物を持つ
itsukara omotai nimotsu o motsu
carrying a heavy burden day after day
日々に慣れてしまっていたんだろう
hibi ni nareteshimatteitan darou
Don't worry and set aside all your difficulties
難しいことは後回しでいいから
muzukashii koto wa atomawashide iikara
Night awaits me when I'm lonely
孤独なボクを夜が待つ
kodoku na boku o yoru ga matsu
Please don't make me feel lonely anymore
寂しい思いはもうボクにはさせないでよ
sabishii omoi wa mou boku ni wa sasenaideyo
Please don't seek solitude
思い出した夜を
omoidashita yoru o
when you remember that night
どうかひとりぼっちとは呼ばないで
douka hitori bocchito wa yobanaide
If you are weak
あなたが弱いのなら
anata ga yowai no nara
I'll show my weakness
ボクの弱さも見せるから
boku no yowasa mo miserukara
And if you pretend to be strong,
あなたが強がるのならば
anata ga tsuyogaru nonaraba
I'll gently embrace your weakness
キミの弱さをそっと抱きしめるよ
kimi no yowasa o sotto dakishimeruyo
I won't leave you alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaiyo