[KAGE]
Hey!
Let's hurry up and get going!
[DESPA]
My apologies for the delay.
Now, off we go to celebrate the
completion of Bojji's training!
Let us gorge ourselves
on some fine local fare!
- [BOJJI] Au!
- [KAGE] Yeah!
Huh? Hold on, Bojji.
Is that... a sword?
[BOJJI]
Hmm.
But it looks like it's
practically the size of you.
Can you actually swing
something that big?
[KAGE]
Whoa-ho-ho! That's awesome!
[BOJJI]
Hmm! Hm, hm, hm!
Au!
[KAGE]
Whoa!
Huh?
Uh. Huh? Huh?!
Huh...?!
Tears mingled with sweat
その涙が汗が滲んだ
sono namida ga ase ga nijinda
With your own unique beauty
誰とも違う美しさで
dare to mo chigau utsukushisa de
Smile for me
笑っておくれよ
waratte okureyo
Running out of breath, you're more wonderful than everyone else
息を切らした君は 誰より素敵さ
iki o kirashita kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Ranking of Kings
Almost melting into those listless days
気の抜けた炭酸みたいに
ki no nuketa tansan mitai ni
Feeling drained of energy like a flat soda
微かに気怠い日々に溶けた
kasuka ni kedarui hibi ni toketa
As a duckling, spread your wings,
家鴨の侭で翼を広げて
ahiru no mama de tsubasa o hirogete
dream of becoming a swan and soar through the sky
空を舞う白鳥の夢をみる
sora o mau shiratori no yume o miru
Put in your best effort rather than straying from the path
彷徨うくらいなら 一層味わい尽くしましょ
samayou kurai nara issou ajiwai tsukushimasho
For there's nothing fun about taking shortcuts, right?
近道ばかりじゃ 味気がないでしょ
chikamichi bakarija ajike ga naidesho
You took your time, choosing to take the hard road
道草を食って 泥濘み飲んで
michikusa o kutte nukarumi nonde
But you couldn't get there
でも辿り着けなくて
demo tadori tsukenakute
You keep chasing the sunset as many times as it takes
また何度だって 夕暮れを追いかけるの
mata nando datte yuugure o oikakeruno
Now run ahead
走れ遥か先へ
hashire haruka saki e
Your dirty shoes and footprints will definitely head towards the future
汚れた靴と足跡は 確かに未来へと
yogoreta kutsu to ashiato wa tashika ni mirai e to
Charging forward, running out of breath
今駆けてゆく 息を切らした
ima kaketeyuku iki o kirashita
You're more wonderful than everyone else
君は誰より素敵さ
kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Episode 10
The Prince's Sword
[KAGE grunts] That's not
a sword, it's a needle!
You fraud!
You just gave him
a little rinky-dink sword
in a giant sheath to make it
look like he'd gotten stronger!
I've done exactly as
I said I would do,
and you've missed the point
of the scabbard, as well!
You see, it creates
an impression of strength.
[KAGE]
What?! "Missed the point?"
How's that any different
from what I said, huh?!
[DESPA]
Bojji.
There will always be people
who look down upon you,
no matter what you
might accomplish.
Will you doubt yourself
and look at the ground?
Or will you meet their gaze?
[BOJJI gasps]
Enough already.
You know how to give a nice
pep talk, but this is reality!
[DESPA] Hmm. I assure you
it's not just talk, Kage.
Bojji is far more capable
than you realize.
[DESPA]
And what's more,
if even you don't believe
in him, then who will?
[KAGE]
Uh. You're right...
What's gotten into me?
[KAGE]
Bojji...
I'm sorry for doubting
you like that.
Ah...
[KAGE]
Still...
[KAGE] What really
happened in that chamber?
[BOJJI]
Mm.
Much obliged.
- [KAGE] Thank you.
- [BOJJI] Au.
[KAGE] Anyway, is that
little needle-sword
really gonna be
any help in a fight?
[DESPA] It will be plenty.
If this theory of mine is right,
Bojji is nigh
untouchable in battle.
Untouchable, eh?
I like the sound of that!
[BOJJI chuckles]
Now, then. Let us
raise a glass to Bojji
and his mastery of
the Despa arts!
To Bojji!
- Au!
- [KAGE] Cheers!
The Despa arts, huh?
Tell me all about it.
[CUSTOMER 10A]
Ah― Ah, hey!
You three again? Do you plan
to pick a fight with me
every time I come to eat here?
[ABAN gulping]
I'm Aban, the eldest!
I'm the middle one, Layne!
I'm Boan, the youngest!
[PATRONS gasping]
[CAPTAIN 05A] The rough
and rowdy Aban Brothers
just walked in!
Well, well. Who's
your buddy, there?
My apprentice in the art
of swordsmanship.
[LAYNE]
"Swordsmanship"?
[BOAN]
Your apprentice?
You mean this little
pipsqueak right here?
[laughter]
[KAGE] Hey! Who are you guys
callin' a pipsqueak?
[ABAN] What? You have
a problem with that, friend?
Now, now. Do not rise
to their bait.
[KAGE] That's a shock.
Despa's playing it cool.
[KAGE]
And Bojji, too!
I guess that is the mature way
to handle these guys.
[KAGE]
Yeah. Play it cool...
When I think about it,
he's a perfect apprentice.
For a camel-faced blowhard
like you, that is.
[laughter]
[DESPA gasps]
- [ABAN groans]
- [CUSTOMER 10B yelps]
[KAGE] What the heck?!
Hey, Despa!
You can mock my apprentice
all you like,
but you will not
insult my appearance!
Other way around!
[CUSTOMER 10B yelps]
[ABAN]
That was a mistake.
En garde!
- [ABAN growls]
- [DESPA groans]
[BOJJI]
Ah...
[DESPA groans]
[LAYNE]
Heh.
- [BOAN] Hmph!
- [DESPA groans]
He's weak! Real weak!
You're done for!
[gasps]
Ah!
[BOJJI groans]
[PATRONS gasping]
[FEMALE CUSTOMER 1A0 shrieks]
Bojji!
Uh?
[KAGE]
Whoa! You're back and... look!
Is there even a bruise on you?
[BOJJI]
Hmph.
Ah!
[ABAN]
What a joke.
You looking for a fight,
little boy?
Bojji! He's too big.
Use your sword!
[DESPA] No. There's no need for
him to draw his weapon.
[gasps]
[DESPA] He will dispatch
his opponent barehanded.
Despa, how hard did you
get hit with that tray?
Have faith and observe.
[KAGE]
Huh?!
You think you can
mess with me, runt?!
[growls]
[ABAN]
Uh...
What was that?
His punch didn't do
anything to him!
[chuckles]
[KAGE]
Wait. He's laughing?
Bojji landed a punch
and he's laughing?
[ABAN groaning]
[KAGE]
Huh?!
- [PATRONS gasping]
- [DESPA] Hmm.
[CUSTOMER]
Did you see that?
- [LAYNE, BOAN] Aban!
- [BOJJI sighs]
[ABAN]
Stay back!
What the hell
did you do to me, kid...?
How did he do that?
As living creatures,
we have weak points
throughout our bodies.
We'll pound you!
Little runt!
[DESPA]
Take the jaw, for instance.
Even a relatively light blow
can jolt the brain hard enough
to induce a concussion.
Bojji can do that?
[DESPA] To make up for
his own lack of power,
he utilizes his foe's momentum―
and lands a precise hit
to their weak spot.
This is the
magnificence of Bojji.
[KAGE]
Despa!
You really are a genius!
[sniffles]
I'll never doubt you again!
Right.
You little creep...
What kinda trick did you pull?!
- [KAGE gasps]
- Hold it right there!
Since you've taken
your weapon in hand,
are you ready and willing
to escalate this petty squabble
into a fight to the death?
Say what?
[DESPA]
Bojji!
[BOJJI grunts]
Draw your blade!
[ABAN snarls]
Little bastard!
[KAGE gasps]
[BOTH whimpering]
Gah!
[BOTH]
Get up, Brother!
[KAGE whimpers]
Bojji just killed that guy!
Expertly done.
He's out cold,
but very much alive.
[BOJJI gasps]
Bojji knocked him out?!
[DESPA] Now get him
out of here, you louts.
[KAGE]
I still don't get it.
How did Bojji take him down?
[DESPA]
Mm. Allow me to explain.
Owie!
[KAGE]
Eh? Did that even hurt?
Yes...
Though the needle may not
have pierced my skin,
it did prick a pain receptor.
"Receptor"?
Indeed. And conversely...!
[KAGE]
Waugh!
- What?! Why?!
- [wailing]
- What did you do?!
- [whimpering]
- [wailing]
I'm completely fine.
[KAGE]
Huh?!
If you avoid the pain receptors,
it doesn't hurt in the least.
I didn't break any
blood vessels, either.
Can you stop?
That's really gross-looking.
Living creatures are marvels.
We are complex, and complex
things have many points
of failure, which Bojji
has learned quite well.
To knock an opponent
unconscious, one must cause
the brain to fail momentarily.
[KAGE]
Huh?
[DESPA] One can bring
the brain to a gentle halt
by briefly cutting off
the flow of blood.
With his needle-sword,
Bojji can stimulate his foe's
nerve endings directly,
while avoiding
their vital organs,
causing their blood
vessels to dilate.
The resulting drop in blood
pressure starves the brain
of oxygen, leading to
loss of consciousness.
[KAGE]
Uh... Huh...?
Put simply, Bojji has the
ability to incapacitate
an opponent without
causing lasting damage.
[KAGE gasps]
That's so cool!
That's awesome, Bojji!
This sword style
is perfect for you!
[DESPA] Furthermore...
Using that same skill,
he can bring the machinery of
an opponent's body
to a permanent halt
with minimal exertion.
[KAGE]
Whoa... Bojji...
You really have gotten stronger.
I should be happy, right?
[DESPA chuckles]
A-Are you not?
Kage, what kind of strength
have you been searching for
- all this time?
- [KAGE] Huh?
And in the pursuit of
this great strength,
is your intention not
to protect others?
The sword of a king,
able to save the meek
and shame the mighty.
Is this not exactly the power
you've been seeking?
Y-You're right. I did want that!
But still, powerful people
can have weak hearts.
[DESPA]
Don't worry.
Bojji will not be
corrupted by his strength.
Mental fortitude was the
foundation of his training.
Bojji. One who bears a sword
must obey three rules.
Rule one!
Au, au!
[KAGE]
Huh?
Rule two!
[BOJJI]
Awau, au!
[DESPA]
Rule three!
[BOJJI]
Au, awah!
[DESPA] Hmm! You must etch
those words into your soul!
[BOJJI]
Ah!
[DESPA chuckles]
[KAGE sobs] Bojji...
I'm so proud right now!
Thank you, Despa!
Catch those?
Nope.
Ultimately, Bojji's strength
comes from the righteousness
already in his heart.
Yeah, he's exactly right!
Bojji, you're amazing!
Au-ah.
[DESPA] So long as you always
bear those rules firmly in mind,
your abilities will only grow.
As will your strength
in body and mind.
Ah!
[DESPA] You will lead
a joyous existence that shines
like a beacon to others.
- Ah!
- [DESPA] Indeed!
Ever onward!
- Au, au, au.
- Thank you for everything,
Despa!
Now, then...
Shall we feast, gentlemen?
[KAGE sighs]
I'm totally stuffed!
[DESPA] Hmm. Uh, why don't the
two of you go ahead without me?
There's one small matter
I need to attend to.
[KAGE]
Huh? See ya, then.
[CAPTAIN 05A]
Attention!
[DESPA] Oh. Please,
that's entirely unnecessary.
[CAPTAIN 05A]
At ease.
[gasps]
Sorry about that.
We didn't need to go for
the face a second time.
But you did, which is exactly
what I asked you to do,
and I got to see how Bojji
performs in real combat.
[DESPA]
For your trouble.
I cannot accept!
Oh, can't you?
Hmm...
[chuckles]
I have to confess,
I didn't expected to be
so completely outmatched.
[DESPA]
Hmm...
The moment he grabbed his sword,
I realized right away
I couldn't beat him.
[CAPTAIN 05A] Then you've got
work to do when we get back.
Huh?!
Give me a break
just this once, Captain!
[CAPTAIN 05A laughing]
[DESPA chuckles]
Though, in truth, today offered
barely a glimpse
of Bojji's true power.
[CAPTAIN 05A]
What?!
Oh, yes, he's acquired
another skill
that's even more impressive.
[DESPA] Though I don't expect
he's going to be putting it
on display terribly often.
[KAGE] Hey Bojji.
When I think about it,
I know you learned how to strike
your opponents' weak spots
thanks to Despa's training,
but you've always been quick.
How in the world
did you get so fast?
[BOJJI]
Au.
Au, au.
Huh? Mitsumata taught you?
You mean, the big snake?
Au!
Good, Prince. Nicely done.
[BOJJI]
Hmm.
Even so, you've much to learn.
[BOJJI]
Ah...
You are still relying
on your eyes.
You must sharpen
your other senses.
[MITSUMATA]
Until your sense of touch...
...can detect
even unseen hazards...
...through the movement of
the air against your skin.
Au!
[BEBIN]
News from the castle?
A pack of underworld
monsters attacked
Queen Hiling's chambers.
Dorshe put his life at
hazard to protect her.
After that, it appears the
Mirror left for the Underworld.
King Bosse has taken no action.
At the moment, Master Apeas
is standing guard
over the Underworld portal.
[BEBIN sighs] There's no way
I can do this alone.
Why do you speak
as if we weren't here?
[laughs] I am the Snake Handler,
and you're all more precious
to me than words can say.
I don't want you in harm's way.
[MITSUMATA]
For you, Master Bebin...
...we would do anything.
[BEBIN]
And Prince Bojji?
Yes. I'm told that
his training is now complete,
and that he's grown a great deal
stronger in the process.
Despa is a master of his craft.
[MITSUMATA]
Indeed. He is.
[BEBIN]
Hmm. So, then...
Prince Bojji...
Master?
[BEBIN] I understand that
you owe quite a heavy debt
to Prince Bojji.
Even so, I believe
Prince Daida is more fit
for the throne by far.
And it seems I'm not
alone in that belief.
Your decision to train Bojji
and teach him to read lips
has been met with skepticism.
It's true. Prince Bojji's
strength may never rise
to the caliber of a king.
And yet...
As the boy grows,
I know with certainty that
he will save many people.
In fact... Prince Daida himself
will be counted among them.
Prince Bojji will save
Prince Daida?
[laughs] Is that a prophecy
or wild intuition?
I couldn't say...
Just a feeling,
but one I do not doubt.
[BEBIN]
Hmm...
The king's return...
That may well be where
this all ends up.
Well, if Mitsumata is the one
who trained you, then...
...that means Bebin probably
knows what's going on.
[BOJJI]
Huh?
It's like this. Bebin told me
this before we left the castle.
Apparently, your kingdom
has gotten wrapped up
in some huge conspiracy.
[gasps]
Au, ah?!
No, and I have no idea
how it's gonna play out.
But... he told me
I needed to keep you safe.
Know this. I serve King Daida.
My loyalty is to him above all
others and I have no intention
of handing his crown
over to Prince Bojji.
In time, you'll come to
understand why I would do this.
So, Bojji... Where
do we go from here?
Will you return to your kingdom?
[gasps]
[KAGE]
Huh...?
Hey, buddy.
Something's troubling you.
You think that old biddy
tried to do you in?
[KAGE'S MOTHER]
My dear Kage...
[KAGE gasps]
[KAGE] Bojji!
Where's your courage gone?!
[gasps]
[sniffles]
The courage to put
your faith in others!
[BOJJI gasps]
[sobs]
- [BOJJI grunting]
- [KAGE gasps]
Hey. Wait!
[KAGE]
Stop! Bojji!
[BOJJI grunting]
[BOJJI]
Heh...
Hey, bud. You okay?
[BOJJI]
Au...
[KAGE gasps]
[KAGE]
All right, then.
Let's go home, Bojji!
[BOJJI]
Ah!
Please don't leave me alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないでよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaideyo
Since when did I start getting used to
いつから重たい荷物を持つ
itsukara omotai nimotsu o motsu
carrying a heavy burden day after day
日々に慣れてしまっていたんだろう
hibi ni nareteshimatteitan darou
Don't worry and set aside all your difficulties
難しいことは後回しでいいから
muzukashii koto wa atomawashide iikara
Night awaits me when I'm lonely
孤独なボクを夜が待つ
kodoku na boku o yoru ga matsu
Please don't make me feel lonely anymore
寂しい思いはもうボクにはさせないでよ
sabishii omoi wa mou boku ni wa sasenaideyo
Please don't seek solitude
思い出した夜を
omoidashita yoru o
when you remember that night
どうかひとりぼっちとは呼ばないで
douka hitori bocchito wa yobanaide
If you are weak
あなたが弱いのなら
anata ga yowai no nara
I'll show my weakness
ボクの弱さも見せるから
boku no yowasa mo miserukara
And if you pretend to be strong,
あなたが強がるのならば
anata ga tsuyogaru nonaraba
I'll gently embrace your weakness
キミの弱さをそっと抱きしめるよ
kimi no yowasa o sotto dakishimeruyo
I won't leave you alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaiyo