[DAIDA] We played together often
when we were very young.
But later, as I
started to grow...
[HILING] Your brother Bojji
is a pitiable child,
feeble in body and mind.
Helpless on his own.
[HILING]
And for this reason,
it is your duty to become strong
enough to protect him, Daida.
Do you understand?
I won't fail you, Mother!
[DAIDA] After that,
I first met the Mirror.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
How do you do?
It's talking! This mirror talks!
[DAIDA] I could count on it to
provide me with valuable advice.
And also, with the praise
I so desired.
[MAGIC MIRROR] You are among
the chosen, Prince Daida.
One of the few born into
this world destined to reign
over its people as their king.
[DAIDA] Soon... without
realizing it myself...
...I came to see
my brother as a weakling.
Tears mingled with sweat
その涙が汗が滲んだ
sono namida ga ase ga nijinda
With your own unique beauty
誰とも違う美しさで
dare to mo chigau utsukushisa de
Smile for me
笑っておくれよ
waratte okureyo
Running out of breath, you're more wonderful than everyone else
息を切らした君は 誰より素敵さ
iki o kirashita kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Ranking of Kings
Almost melting into those listless days
気の抜けた炭酸みたいに
ki no nuketa tansan mitai ni
Feeling drained of energy like a flat soda
微かに気怠い日々に溶けた
kasuka ni kedarui hibi ni toketa
As a duckling, spread your wings,
家鴨の侭で翼を広げて
ahiru no mama de tsubasa o hirogete
dream of becoming a swan and soar through the sky
空を舞う白鳥の夢をみる
sora o mau shiratori no yume o miru
Put in your best effort rather than straying from the path
彷徨うくらいなら 一層味わい尽くしましょ
samayou kurai nara issou ajiwai tsukushimasho
For there's nothing fun about taking shortcuts, right?
近道ばかりじゃ 味気がないでしょ
chikamichi bakarija ajike ga naidesho
You took your time, choosing to take the hard road
道草を食って 泥濘み飲んで
michikusa o kutte nukarumi nonde
But you couldn't get there
でも辿り着けなくて
demo tadori tsukenakute
You keep chasing the sunset as many times as it takes
また何度だって 夕暮れを追いかけるの
mata nando datte yuugure o oikakeruno
Now run ahead
走れ遥か先へ
hashire haruka saki e
Your dirty shoes and footprints will definitely head towards the future
汚れた靴と足跡は 確かに未来へと
yogoreta kutsu to ashiato wa tashika ni mirai e to
Charging forward, running out of breath
今駆けてゆく 息を切らした
ima kaketeyuku iki o kirashita
You're more wonderful than everyone else
君は誰より素敵さ
kimi wa dare yori suteki sa
Episode 11
Older and Younger Brothers
[DAIDA]
Bebin.
[BEBIN]
Yes?
Must we go to such
lengths to accommodate
my weakling of a brother?
Do you think Prince
Bojji is a weakling?
What, then?
Is he not?
[BEBIN]
It's been a while, Prince Daida.
Would you care
to visit town with me?
[DAIDA]
Hmm.
[BOYS giggling]
[BOY 11B]
Hey, what's over there?
[MAN coughing]
[DAIDA]
Why did we come here?
[SORII] A chance to see
the people of the kingdom
up close, perhaps?
[DAIDA]
Pointless.
[SORII] A chance to explore
some hypotheticals, then.
[DAIDA]
"Hypotheticals"?
Consider this.
Would you like to live
100 years, Prince Daida?
A hundred...
Don't be absurd!
Who'd want to live that long?!
That being the case,
is the idea of living
90 years more appealing?
Or is that still
too long for your liking?
Sorii... What are
you getting at?
[SORII chuckles]
Only making idle chatter.
I beg your pardon.
Prince Daida.
I believe I've spotted someone
you'd call a weakling.
One far worse off
than Prince Bojji.
Worse off in what way?
Neither of them can hear,
but your brother is
the more fortunate.
That man is blind.
[gasps]
Why, then...?
Why would one
carry on existing like that?
To bear that burden...
To survive on pity!
I would sooner end my own life
than live that way.
I see. Then fate has
set greater challenges
before him than you
are willing to face.
Fair to say?
And yet, this man you'd
call weak is pressing on
when you say you would not.
That's just doublespeak!
I meant...
If you could ask him, I doubt
he would think anything of
the burden you describe.
He's been able to carry on
living despite his afflictions.
For that...
...he can thank your father,
and the prosperous kingdom
he's built.
[growls]
Prince Daida. Our
goal is to instill in you
the strength to bring hope
to everyone else.
[DAIDA growls]
I was... a fool.
[sobbing]
[gasps]
You there!
Where'd you come from?!
Can you get back?!
Don't be afraid.
We're going to get
out of here together.
[GIRL]
I didn't do anything wrong.
- I did nothing!
- [gasps]
[GIRL]
I'm scared... Help me!
Please stop. It hurts...
I'm so hungry...
"Please stop"?! Did you listen
when we said that?!
Heinous villain!
How could someone be so cruel?!
All this misery is on your head!
[MAN 11C]
Apologize!
- [GIRL] No, I didn't!
- [MAN 11D] You abomination!
[GIRL]
It's not true!
[gasps]
Your hands!
Ah! What... is this?!
[GIRLS]
Liars! They're all lying!
I don't understand any of this!
[WOMAN 11A]
That girl you see...
That monster killed all of us.
[gasps]
[WOMAN 11A]
Us and so many more!
Our deaths were painful...
The suffering was unbearable.
Our land was peaceful.
Great and plentiful.
Our people, marked
by kindness and wisdom.
But then...
[WOMAN 11A] They invaded our
domain, and what little they
didn't tear asunder,
they stole for themselves!
[GIRLS]
No! That isn't true!
Stop it!
Ah!
[GIRL]
My mask... It's gone...
- [laughter]
- [DAIDA gasps]
- [GIRL] Where is my mask?
- [laughter continues]
- Where is it...?
- Where did it go? Please...
- [laughter continues]
- I'm scared...
[DAIDA]
Here.
- Ah!
- [GIRL] That's mine!
What... are you?!
Your face is...
Monster. You monster!
[GIRL]
You're wrong! I'm not!
I'm a little girl. And one day,
I'm going to be a princess!
[sobbing]
[DAIDA grunts]
[WOMAN 11B]
She's quite hideous, isn't she?
[WOMAN 11A]
We made her that way.
[MAN 11B]
With our own hands.
You did it?!
We flayed the skin from her
face so all who look at her
will see the mark of her sin!
And we cut off her hands
to prevent her from resisting.
- [DAIDA whimpers]
- [GIRL sobbing]
[gasps]
[sobbing continues]
[DAIDA whimpering]
[DAIDA snarls]
[MAN 11E whimpers]
Wait!
[MAN 11B]
Stop this!
[blows thudding]
[DAIDA]
Hey!
They're gone now.
I'm Daida. You?
[GIRL]
Miranjo.
Miranjo. Don't let them
bring you down.
I'm on your side.
She has been stained
with the blood of hundreds
of victims like us.
These are her just desserts.
We have a right to retribution.
Tch! Enough!
If you want her, then fight me!
[MIRANJO]
That smell...
Do it!
[DAIDA gasps]
They vanished.
[MIRANJO] Have you ever
met a man named "Bosse"?
What's that?
[MIRANJO]
You have the same smell as him.
His smell?
[sniffs]
Does that mean... you also
know my father somehow?
Your father? Bosse is your dad?
Ah.
He must be somebody else.
The Bosse I know
has no children.
More to the point,
how did you get in here?
I'm trying to find a way out.
I see.
[MIRANJO]
Thank you for coming to save me.
Goodbye.
[DAIDA]
Wait.
You should stay with me.
It'll be safer that way.
[MIRANJO gasps]
What's wrong? Speak up.
[MIRANJO]
Oh. It's nothing.
[DAIDA]
Hmm... No need to worry.
My mother will be coming
to get me out of here soon.
[MIRANJO]
Get you out?
[DAIDA] That's right.
And you'll be coming with me.
[MIRANJO]
I will?
We're going to get
out of this place together.
I swear it. Stay with me.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
What is this...?
It's as though a weight
was lifted from my heart.
[gasps]
[grunting]
Wait here a moment.
[SERVANT 11A snoring]
Huh...? Hah...?
Gah! King Desha!
Open it.
[SERVANT 11A]
Yes, sire!
[DESHA]
Hmm? Huh...
Gah! Empty?! But how?!
[DESHA]
Hmm...
[SERVANT 11A]
Guh...
[DESHA sniffs] A faint
lingering smell of death.
[growls]
King Desha... I've failed you!
You haven't done any such thing.
This has been set into
motion by outside forces,
making use of a power
we'd thought lost until now.
[SERVANT 11A]
A lost power, sire?
Should that power
reach the surface,
it would become
a problem for all of us.
The Order of the
Underworld's commander. Ouken.
A man whose fighting
techniques defy explanation,
known throughout our
land as the Sword King.
[grunts]
Summon the captain!
[SERVANT 11A gasps]
Yes, sire!
Onward. Quickly!
[DORSHE panting]
Please wait, Your Majesty.
[wheezing]
He's not built for this.
We'll rest once
we reach the top.
[HILING]
Be strong, Daida.
I have Dorshe with me,
along with these
hardened soldiers.
We're coming.
[DOMAS]
Hokuro!
Is even this beyond you?
[panting]
- [DOMAS grunting]
- [gasps]
[grunting]
It works splendidly...
[HOKURO]
Could he be any worse a teacher?
He only knows
how to train himself!
If I want to learn the sword,
I'll have to learn it
my own way.
- What's on your mind?
- [HOKURO squeals]
[DOMAS]
The day we seal the gate
to the Underworld
is approaching.
[HOKURO]
Huh?
King Bosse told me to expect
some event to signal us
when the time arrives.
That's it? Did he say
anything more specific?
He said no more
than what I told you.
Hmm... This all feels ominous.
Agreed.
I don't understand.
It almost seems like King Bosse
is covering for someone.
But for who?
Not sure.
Lady Miranjo...
[metal clanging]
[APEAS whimpering]
[grunting]
[APEAS grunts, groans]
Lady Miranjo, I can't!
[screeches]
[APEAS grunts]
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[APEAS whimpering]
[MIRANJO] What are you
so afraid of, Apeas?
Perhaps your confidence
has been stolen away by those
who lacked confidence in you?
I've grown to like you
quite a bit since we first met.
[APEAS gasps]
Yours is such a tender heart,
and so easily hurt.
But for this, you readily
understand the pain of others
and that endears you to me.
Look at me.
[APEAS gasps]
Most of what you see was
not born, but fabricated.
[APEAS gasps]
My smile has no warmth.
But you are a growing being
with boundless potential.
Simply envision
the man you wish to become.
Have faith in me, and believe
in yourself as I believe in you.
[APEAS whimpering]
[MIRANJO]
There, there.
Your wounds will take time
to heal, as all wounds do.
[APEAS sobbing]
[MIRANJO]
But slowly, little by little,
you will become stronger.
[APEAS]
I've been expecting you,
Lady Miranjo.
[DESHA] It would appear
the escaped criminals have fled
to the Kingdom of Bosse.
You must capture them
immediately, without fail.
Furthermore, with old Bosse's
passing, his nation was left
on the verge of civil war.
So, accordingly...
...when we capture the
fugitives, we'll also be
capturing the Kingdom of Bosse!
[KAGE]
Thanks for everything!
You've done so much
for us, Despa!
I'm more grateful to you
than I know how to put in words.
Au!
I've enjoyed our time
together, too.
[KAGE] We'll be back
to visit, all right?
[DESPA]
You're welcome any time.
Ah-au, awaw, ah-deh-dah.
Awa, dau.
No need to fret.
We will meet again.
Come to think of it, when
exactly did you come up with
a way to understand Bojji?
Oh. I never did that.
[BOJJI, KAGE]
Huh?!
I don't know a bit
of sign language.
Ah... A-Ah...
Wait. What about those rules
for carrying a sword?
[inaudible]
Well, yes. Of course I
would recognize the words
I'd had him recite
back to me every day.
"Understand"
is a stretch.
[laughs]
[whimpering]
[DESPA]
Ah. Even so. Bojji...
Please believe me when
I say that your gratitude could
hardly be more apparent.
I should thank you as well.
Teaching you has been
immensely rewarding.
Know this. You may feel
weaker for what you lack,
but in fact, its absence could
be a source of strength.
[BOJJI]
Huh?
[DESPA] It has led you to chart
your own path through the world,
a path most people
could never hope to walk.
And though your journey
has been painful at times,
through your experience
you've grown strong enough
to see it through.
Bojji, you should love
everything about yourself.
[whimpers]
[KAGE whimpering]
Courage!
- Au!
- Courage!
Bye, Despa!
We'll always be grateful!
[BOJJI]
Ah-wa, au!
Of course.
[rumbling]
Someone's here!
[horse neighs]
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Whoa, whoa.
[KAGE] Jeez! Did you really
need to send this many guys?!
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Prince Bojji, please hop on.
Huh? What's this?
They're giving us a ride?
Actually. A group of
underworld criminals escaped,
and they're believed to have
entered the Kingdom of Bosse.
Whoa. Seems like scary stuff!
King Desha has
deployed these soldiers
to pursue said criminals.
Please allow them
to bring you along.
[CAPTAIN 5A] Quickly!
There's no time to waste.
[BOJJI]
Mm!
Goodbye and godspeed
to both of you.
[KAGE]
Whoo! We're really movin'!
This feels great!
Au, au, au-au. Au!
We'll be back at the castle way
sooner than I thought we would!
[BOJJI]
Au!
When we capture the fugitives,
we'll also be capturing
the Kingdom of Bosse!
[KAGE]
Hey, Captain!
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Hmm?! Ahem. What is it?
Uh, just wondering.
What kind of underworld
criminals are we
dealing with, exactly?
[CAPTAIN 5A]
A fair question.
Vicious, violent brutes,
each and every one.
Black the Brunet
and Red the Copperhead.
Professional killers.
The massive Gigan,
bearing a terribly powerful,
metal-clad body.
The bandit Zokku, leader
of the hoards of brigands
roaming the Underworld.
The Almighty Kingbo, long
since fallen from the throne.
And lastly, the Sword King of
the Underworld, Ouken.
Each is frightfully
powerful in his own right.
[BOJJI gasps]
Au, au! Au, dah, awa!
[KAGE]
Huh?
[CAPTAIN 5A]
What did Prince Bojji say?
[KAGE] He asked if old bitty―
I-I mean, if the queen is okay.
[CAPTAIN 5A]
I dearly hope she is.
But for now, we have
no way of knowing.
He doesn't know.
Ah...
Easy. It's gonna be okay, Bojji!
With your Despa Arts,
you can take these clowns on,
no problem!
Au!
Now let's get moving, Captain!
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Hmm! Faster!
Hyah!
[HILING]
Ah.
There's something
unusual going on here.
[DORSHE]
You there! What's happening?
[gasps]
Master Dorshe!
Well, sir...
Six men appeared in
the castle out of nowhere,
and they quickly took
King Bosse captive.
He was captured?!
They took him alive?!
There's no way.
Who are these six men?
[SOLDIER 11A]
We don't know.
To the castle!
[horse whinnies]
[DORSHE gasps]
Your Majesty!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
So you've come...
...Hiling.
Please don't leave me alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないでよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaideyo
Since when did I start getting used to
いつから重たい荷物を持つ
itsukara omotai nimotsu o motsu
carrying a heavy burden day after day
日々に慣れてしまっていたんだろう
hibi ni nareteshimatteitan darou
Don't worry and set aside all your difficulties
難しいことは後回しでいいから
muzukashii koto wa atomawashide iikara
Night awaits me when I'm lonely
孤独なボクを夜が待つ
kodoku na boku o yoru ga matsu
Please don't make me feel lonely anymore
寂しい思いはもうボクにはさせないでよ
sabishii omoi wa mou boku ni wa sasenaideyo
Please don't seek solitude
思い出した夜を
omoidashita yoru o
when you remember that night
どうかひとりぼっちとは呼ばないで
douka hitori bocchito wa yobanaide
If you are weak
あなたが弱いのなら
anata ga yowai no nara
I'll show my weakness
ボクの弱さも見せるから
boku no yowasa mo miserukara
And if you pretend to be strong,
あなたが強がるのならば
anata ga tsuyogaru nonaraba
I'll gently embrace your weakness
キミの弱さをそっと抱きしめるよ
kimi no yowasa o sotto dakishimeruyo
I won't leave you alone
ひとりぼっちにはさせないよ
hitori bocchi ni wa sasenaiyo