[MAGIC MIRROR] What I want is
to bring this country to ruin.
[gasping]
That's absurd!
You've lost your mind!
[MAGIC MIRROR chuckles]
On the contrary,
I am seeing a long-held
wish realized.
[DORSHE] So the rumors
I heard back then were true.
She played some part in
the death of the former queen.
Apeas! Why are you
following that woman?!
[APEAS] Don't call her
"that woman!"
I... have sworn undying
loyalty to Lady Miranjo!
[DORSHE]
What?!
[MONSTERS growling]
[gasping]
[MAGIC MIRROR chuckles]
[growling]
[DORSHE grunting]
[KNIGHT 3 groaning]
[ANN grunts]
[KNIGHT 3 grunts]
Hah! What's this? These things
are hardly a real threat!
- [ANN] Don't be a fool.
- [BOTH gasp]
Ann the knight
[ANN] The beasts
have only been testing
the reach of your weapons.
It's hardly begun.
Ann...
[ANN]
You needn't worry, Hiling.
The enemy shall not
lay a finger on you.
We will protect you
as we've always done.
- [grunting]
- [growling]
[OUKEN rasping]
Even now, there is someone choking back tears
誰かが変な涙を 飲み込んで 呑み込んでいる
dareka ga hen na namida wo nomikonde nomikondeiru
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力がこの裏 悪意振り解いて
chikara ga kono ura akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
Look out for these tiny hands
小さなこの手は今
chiisana kono te wa ima
Everything I've fallen in love with
愛してしまった全部全部
aishiteshimatta zenbu zenbu
Including all the curses that have befallen me
降りかかった呪いも全部
furikakatta noroi mo zenbu
All of my feelings for my loved ones
もう愛してしまった想いを全部
mou aishiteshimatta omoi wo zenbu
Give me enough light to protect them
守れるほどの光を
mamoreru hodo no hikari wo
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力が伴う悪意振り解いて
chikara ga tomonau akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
The shadows are closing in, asking, "What are you?"
影は迫る"お前はなんだ"と
kage wa semaru "omae wa nanda" to
Ranking of Kings
Episode 13
The Kingdom in Turmoil
[KNIGHT 3 gasps]
[ANN] Assist them.
I'll see to Hiling's safety.
Hiling. You must be prepared
to flee from here at any moment.
Huh?
[ANN]
Hold fast, but be ready.
[DORSHE] They're going
to pounce all at once.
Careful, Dorshe!
[DORSHE]
Hmm.
[gasps]
[grunting]
I learned my lesson
when we fought before.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Impressive.
Yes.
[MAGIC MIRROR] And yet...
I foresee the same end.
Dorshe battered and weary.
Hiling drenched
in her own blood.
They may fight
with all they have,
but this shall be
where they die.
[KNIGHT 4 grunts]
Whoa.
He's killed a few on his own.
We haven't taken one between us.
[KNIGHT 3 gasps]
This is madness.
[ANN]
A war of attrition.
The monsters plan
to wear those three down.
[ANN grunts]
[grunts]
[ANN] But it won't work.
Not against veterans like us.
[BLACK, RED grunt]
Seems like this is
where the fun is at.
[RED chuckles]
[KNIGHT 3]
More trouble?!
Hey, we wanna kill
these three ourselves.
But we don't need to deal
with your monsters.
Make the things back off.
[MAGIC MIRROR] Just as well.
Now they can attack Hiling.
[HILING gasps]
[roaring]
- [KNIGHTS gasping]
- [KNIGHT 4] Why, you--!
- [BLACK grunts]
- [KNIGHT 2 gasps]
- [RED] Hyah!
- [KNIGHT 4] Ah!
No one said that
you could leave.
[chuckles]
[DORSHE snarls]
- [HILING] Dorshe!
- I'll be fine!
[ANN] Don't you dare
let yourselves lose
to a couple of petty thugs.
Crush them!
You should be more than able!
What did you just call us?!
[KNIGHTS yelling]
[BLACK grunting]
[ANN grunts]
[ANN]
I don't think so.
- [grunting]
- [clanging]
[BOTH chuckle]
[gasping]
[GIGAN grunts]
[KNIGHTS groaning]
[GIGAN growls]
[gasping]
[KNIGHTS gasping]
[groaning]
[DORSHE grunts]
[BLACK, RED, GIGAN laughing]
[gasps]
[whistles]
- [whinnying]
- [HILING gasps]
[ANN grunts]
I can't leave you two behind!
[ANN] Fighting is our job.
Now get out of here!
[roaring]
[DORSHE grunts]
Not another step.
[DORSHE gasps]
[ANN]
Not one.
[HILING gasps]
[MAGIC MIRROR laughs]
- [whinnying
- [HILING yelps]
Ow!
[gasps]
- Ah...
- [OUKEN laughs wheezingly]
- [HILING shrieks]
[ANN gasps]
- [DORSHE gasps]
- [GIGAN growls]
[grunts]
[ANN panting]
[ANN]
Hiling!
[HILING whimpering]
[ANN]
Hiling!
I'll be all right.
[BOTH gasp]
[ANN rasps]
[HILING gasps]
[HILING whimpering]
Holy Light!
[OUKEN wheezing]
Normally, that attack would
only have blinded him.
[HILING]
Ann!
- Ah!
- [coughing]
[HILING grunts]
[groaning]
[panting]
Oh― It's okay.
You'll survive.
[wheezing]
[gasps]
[gulping]
[MONSTERS growling]
Daida, my son...
[KAGE]
There's the castle! We're close!
Hurry!
[DORSHE groaning]
[footsteps thudding]
[GIGAN growling]
[DORSHE groans]
[GIGAN growls]
Oof. No way that
didn't do him in.
[MONSTERS growling]
[BLACK] And those two
will die soon enough.
We barely even got
the chance to play!
[RED chuckles]
[BLACK chuckles]
- [MONSTERS growling]
- [HILING whimpering]
[HILING]
No. I can't die.
Not yet.
I still need to save Daida.
[HILING grunts]
[snarls]
[yelps]
[HILING growls]
[shrieks]
[HILING grunts]
[gasps]
[HILING gasps]
Queen Hiling! You have to run!
[gasps]
[HILING grunts]
[HILING grunting]
[APEAS]
Queen Hiling...
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Apeas.
I understand.
You have no reason to share
my hatred for these people.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Indeed. You held them dear.
[APEAS]
Lady Miranjo...
I...
[MAGIC MIRROR]
So be it.
[MAGIC MIRROR] Does Dorshe
have enough left in him
to protect Hiling? Or is his
strength exhausted at last?
For your sake,
I shall wait and see.
Lady Miranjo...
[MAGIC MIRROR] In return,
let this betrayal be the last.
I shall...
[inhales]
Get up, Dorshe!
What the...
[DORSHE gasps]
[DORSHE]
Queen Hiling...
[snarls]
[snarling]
Ah!
[GIGAN groans]
[rasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Ha! Your Majesty!
[gasps]
You're still alive!
[bellowing]
[roaring]
[DORSHE growls]
[grunting]
[BOTH gasping]
[GIGAN]
Huh...?!
- [DORSHE grunting]
- [blows thudding]
[DORSHE huffing]
Huh?!
Haah...!
[bones cracking]
[gasps]
[DORSHE groans]
[huffing]
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmuring]
[SOLDIER 13A]
You're in danger.
You all need to
evacuate right now!
[TOWNSWOMAN 13A] Yes, so you
tell us, but where to?
There are monsters
in the castle?
Aren't you lot meant to deal
with things like that?
- Huh?
Eh?
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmuring]
[gasping]
- [whimpering]
- Get out of there!
[TOWNSPEOPLE gasping]
[screaming, gasping]
[bell tolling]
[OUKEN roars]
[screaming, shrieking]
- [SOLDIERS growling]
- Monster!
[yells]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[gasping]
[DORSHE groaning]
Augh!
Dorshe!
[APEAS whimpering]
[MAGIC MIRROR] Enough of this.
We shall return underground.
[APEAS]
Lady Miranjo...
[MAGIC MIRROR] We have more
intruders to deal with.
[APEAS]
But...
[MAGIC MIRROR] The fate of
these two is decided.
They both face a grisly end.
Will you force yourself to
stand here and bear witness
- to their deaths?
- [APEAS whimpers]
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Let us go.
[APEAS grunts]
I'm sorry...
But I... can't do what
you're asking of me!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
So, then...
You would have me as an enemy.
[APEAS]
I wouldn't. Never, I swear!
Tell me: Why do you want to see
Queen Hiling dead so badly?
[gasps]
Forgive me.
[MAGIC MIRROR] I wish only to be
of assistance to King Bosse.
I wish to make
his dream come true.
But saddled with this family,
he can never hope to achieve it.
They must be eliminated.
[MIRANJO] King Bosse, I implore
you to have another child.
Doing so will allow you
to prolong your life.
[BOSSE]
Hmm. Out of the question.
[MIRANJO grunts]
[BOSSE]
Hmm...
Huh.
Miranjo.
During her lifetime, a giantess
can only bear a single child.
Like the gods themselves,
our race is fated to perish
from this world in time.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
I have discovered someone fit
to be your new queen.
Both her bloodline, and her
talents, are quite excellent.
Miranjo. Why such insistence?
[MAGIC MIRROR] Another heir,
King Bosse, I beg you.
[BOSSE]
Hmm...
[door clacks]
[HILING] Hmm... So this is
going to be my room, then?
Hold on. What is this mirror?
[MAID 09A]
Is something wrong?
I can feel the evil
radiating from this!
Remove it at once!
Right!
[HILING grunts]
Hmm.
[MAGIC MIRROR] King Bosse
has taken King Daida's body
for his own.
Surely, it's more
than Hiling can bear.
Before long, their conflict
will have to be resolved.
Apeas. Your duty is fulfilled.
You are done.
From here on,
it is my battle to fight.
Now let us go.
Ma'am.
[BLACK chuckles]
Huh?
Hey.
[BOTH chuckle]
[DORSHE groaning]
- [bones creaking]
- [growling]
- [HILING whimpering]
- [groaning continues]
[snarling]
[bones cracking]
[screaming]
[CAPTAIN 05A]
Hmm?
- [TOWNSPEOPLE scream]
- [WOMAN] Ah He's gaining on us!
[screaming, wailing]
[CAPTAIN 05A]
Prince Ouken.
Is that one of the criminals?
[gasps]
Prince Bojji's here!
Prince Bojji?
Could it be that the prince
has come back to save us...?
But then... that
soldier with him...
[groaning, whimpering]
Heed my words, Captain.
Even your considerable skill
will not be enough
to defeat Ouken.
You're not to engage him under
any circumstance until I arrive.
[TOWNSPEOPLE screaming, wailing]
[CAPTAIN 05A]
Prince Despa...
[screaming continues]
[CAPTAIN 05A]
I cannot allow this to continue!
Bojji!
[DESPA]
One more thing!
Captain, by his very nature,
Ouken is a perfect
foil for Bojji.
They must not be
allowed to fight!
[CAPTAIN 05A growls]
[CAPTAIN 05A]
You mustn't delay, Prince Bojji.
Please get to the castle
and protect Queen Hiling.
Bojji! He says let him handle
this and go help the old biddy!
Ah-au!
[CAPTAIN 05A] You must be
brought in, Prince Ouken.
No, brought down!
[TOWNSPEOPLE gasping, murmuring]
[CAPTAIN 05A]
Forgive me, King Desha...
I have no choice but to
take the demon's head.
Lady Miranjo...
[MAGIC MIRROR]
What is it?
[gasps]
[RED]
Heh!
[BLACK]
[APEAS gasps]
Lady Miranjo!
- [RED] Hrngh!
- [APEAS grunts]
[groaning]
[gasps]
[RED snarls]
[BLACK panting]
[chuckles]
[MAGIC MIRROR]
What do you intend to do
now that you have me?
Heh! Uh?
Whoa― The hell?
[gasps]
It's gold!
Unreal.
With the power of your alchemy,
I could live like a king!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Ugh. So it's true.
You are no more
than a petty thug.
[BLACK] Sure, and I'd have
no problem cutting you up
here and now.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
I suspect you might.
Say what?
[gasps]
[RED grunts]
[groaning]
What happened?!
[footsteps]
[gasps]
[APEAS snarling]
[sighs]
We can talk this out!
Wh― Hey!
[ZOKKU]
Easy. Just wait.
No need to fight.
My friend, I apologize.
These two get
carried away sometimes.
Can I ask you to let it slide?
Just this once.
[APEAS sighs]
[growls]
Tried to stay ahead today to avoid being swept away
流されまいと先回りした今日を
nagasaremai to sakimawarishita kyou wo
But instead got absorbed by yesterday
昨日が吸い込んだ
kinou ga suikonda
With a sigh, I put my feelings aside for now,
ため息　心を後回しにして今日も
tameiki kokoro wo atomawashi ni shite kyou mo
and today, as usual, you jump in with a smile
笑う君は飛び込んだ
warau kimi wa tobikonda
So I pushed back the deadline I'd decided was final
最後ねって決めてたデッドラインを少し延ばした
saigone tte kimeteta deddorain wo sukoshi nobashita
If the view changes after one more step...
あと一歩で景色が変わるのなら
ato iipo de keshiki ga kawaru nonara
Maybe something would change...
何かが変わるのなら
nanika ga kawaru no nara
Shine brightly with all you've got, even if others may laugh at you,
一番に光れ　笑われても
ichiban ni hikare warawarete mo
because I will be holding your hand
手を繋いでいるから
te wo tsunaideirukara
It can't be just someone, it must be you
誰かじゃなくて　あなたじゃなくちゃ
dareka janakute anata janakucha
Only you can save those tears
その涙は救えない
sono namida wa sukuenai
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
I'll be singing for you, waiting for you
あなたに歌ってる　待ってる
anata ni utatteru matteru
I'll be here, singing and waiting for you
この場所で歌ってる　待ってる
kono basho de utatteru matteru