[KAGE]
Since we're done fighting,
we should probably get these
critters back to their home
in the Underworld.
And Mitsumata mentioned
there was a portal right here
under the castle, so we
don't have all that far to go.
There's a portal
in the basement?
Why was I not aware of it?
Absolutely ridiculous.
Master Kage. Having decided
that, you must act quickly.
Master Domas is on his way
to seal the portal as we speak.
[KAGE]
Eh?!
And why would Domas do that?
He is acting upon
King Bosse's orders.
Then it's only safe
to assume he's against us.
Just what could be
the king's ultimate aim?
Bojji.
You may cross paths with Domas.
Are you prepared?
[BOJJI gasps]
[whimpers]
[inaudible]
[KAGE]
Yeah, that'll be tough.
I would have
a hard time facing him.
All right. Chin up.
I know it hurts to remember,
but we still need
to get these guys home.
- Right?
- [BOJJI] Mm!
It's fine. You're not
the kid you were back then.
You're so much
stronger than that now.
[BOJJI]
Hmm.
- [KAGE] And besides...
- Ah?
...I'm here, and we've
all got your back!
[gasps]
Mm!
[KAGE]
Hmm. Well, that's that.
Let's go!
- Yeah!
- [BOJJI] Au!
Prince Bojji, the queen and her
soldiers will need some time
to recover their strength,
so I'll remain with them.
Please allow me
to see to their safety,
and focus on your
task, Prince Bojji.
[BOJJI]
Mm!
And you all can
allow me to see to him.
[DORSHE] He's grown quite
admirably, in such little time.
[HILING]
Yes. Of course.
He's my boy, after all.
Expect no less.
[DOMAS] The Underworld
portal lies through here.
[footsteps thudding]
Huh? Someone is in there.
Hokuro, get back now!
Ah! Yes, sir!
[footsteps grow louder]
- [gasps]
- [grunts]
The Order of the Underworld?!
Even now, there is someone choking back tears
誰かが変な涙を 飲み込んで 呑み込んでいる
dareka ga hen na namida wo nomikonde nomikondeiru
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力がこの裏 悪意振り解いて
chikara ga kono ura akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
Look out for these tiny hands
小さなこの手は今
chiisana kono te wa ima
Everything I've fallen in love with
愛してしまった全部全部
aishiteshimatta zenbu zenbu
Including all the curses that have befallen me
降りかかった呪いも全部
furikakatta noroi mo zenbu
All of my feelings for my loved ones
もう愛してしまった想いを全部
mou aishiteshimatta omoi wo zenbu
Give me enough light to protect them
守れるほどの光を
mamoreru hodo no hikari wo
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力が伴う悪意振り解いて
chikara ga tomonau akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
The shadows are closing in, asking, "What are you?"
影は迫る"お前はなんだ"と
kage wa semaru "omae wa nanda" to
Ranking of Kings
Episode 15
The Order of the Underworld
[SQUAD LEADER]
Who are you?
Domas, of the Kingdom
of Bosse's Big Four.
Standing to.
[SQUAD LEADER]
The Big Four, eh?
Why are you in this castle?
[SQUAD LEADER]
Don't play dumb.
There's no denying your
kingdom infiltrated our castle,
and released our prisoners.
Return them immediately
or prepare to go to war.
Wait, go to war?!
Please, just hold on!
[SQUAD LEADER] You won't be
talking your way out of this.
[DOMAS]
Stop!
[SQUAD LEADER]
You would stand in our way?
[DOMAS grunts]
I have little choice. Such is
the position I find myself in.
[SQUAD LEADER]
You're far outnumbered.
You will die here in vain.
[DOMAS growls]
[SQUAD LEADER]
Out of some misguided
sense of honor, perhaps?
Or rather, is it that you've
simply lost all reason?
[gasps]
Heh.
Come on!
[KNIGHT 15C]
Huh?
[KNIGHT 15A]
Narrowing our approach.
It seems he's kept at least
some reason, Squad Leader.
[SQUAD LEADER] You can take him
with a team of three.
[KNIGHT 15A]
Hmm!
Be careful, Master...
[KNIGHTS yell]
[KNIGHT 15A]
He's stronger than we realized!
[SQUAD LEADER]
What?!
[DOMAS]
I can do this!
[KNIGHT 15A]
Hmm!
[KNIGHT 15C]
Hmph!
[KNIGHT 15B growls]
[DOMAS grunts]
[KNIGHT 15C]
Got you!
[DOMAS grunting]
I'm more than capable of dealing
with all of you by myself!
[gasps]
[KNIGHT 15C gasps]
[KNIGHT 15A]
Is there someone else here?!
I'm your only opponent!
[KNIGHT 15A]
But I'm certain...
[SQUAD LEADER]
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
You're raising your voice
because your nerves
are getting to you. Right, boy?
Know this: Your power can't
save you if you're too tense
to muster it in full.
Fight!
[SQUAD LEADER]
Hmm.
[TSUBUKADE] Squad Leader,
allow me the honor.
[SQUAD LEADER]
Tsubukade? Very well.
[TSUBUKADE]
Sir!
[TSUBUKADE] My blade is
the deadliest in the Underworld!
You swing that
huge sword like a toy.
You must be quite the warrior.
[TSUBUKADE guffaws]
[TSUBUKADE roars]
[DOMAS grunts]
[TSUBUKADE gasps]
Gah!
[SQUAD LEADER]
Ah! He got Tsubukade!
[TSUBUKADE groans]
Uh, thanks, guys.
[SQUAD LEADER] You shouldn't
have been so reckless!
[TSUBUKADE]
Guh, I know, sir. Forgive me.
[DOMAS] He's already recovered
from a blow like that?
[SQUAD LEADER]
Hmm... Tell me―
what was your name again?
[DOMAS]
Domas, of the Big Four.
[SQUAD LEADER]
Why strike him with the spine
of your sword, Domas?
[DOMAS] I'm still not sure
exactly what's happening here.
If possible, I'd rather
avoid any bloodshed.
[SQUAD LEADER]
Then you're taking us lightly.
But... I'm certain
you know better than that.
You don't know what's happening?
And you're not saying that
as a delaying tactic.
No!
I'm entirely in the dark!
[SQUAD LEADER]
Hmph! Here's what I know.
We have a mission,
and you're merely a distraction.
We will bring our strength
to bear and crush our foe!
[KNIGHTS yell]
[SQUAD LEADER growls]
He will learn to fear
the Order of the Underworld.
[DOMAS]
Damn...
[DOMAS grunting]
[grunting continues]
I've come too far
to wimp out now!
You're not going to beat us!
[DOMAS]
Keep out of this!
[KNIGHTS yelling]
[HOKURO]
Master Domas...
During our travels,
we would run and hide
whenever there was danger.
[huffing]
[HOKURO] Was he concealing
his strength all along?
[SQUAD LEADER growls]
[yells]
[DOMAS growls]
[SQUAD LEADER groans]
Well done... boy...
[groans]
[gasps]
[huffing]
Good work, Master!
[gasps]
[HOKURO]
What's that?
This crushing presence I'm
feeling from beyond the door...
[footsteps]
[DOMAS gasps]
[gasps]
[HOKURO]
Ah... Their king!
My spies informed me that
old Bosse passed on recently,
only to return to life by taking
over the body of his second son.
I was told that his forces were
in disarray and the kingdom
was on the verge of collapse.
I didn't anticipate
this kind of resistance.
I expected to reach
Bosse unopposed
and fight him one-on-one.
[DOMAS gasps]
He wanted that...?
[DESHA] Heh... I would assume
you know who I am, knight.
[DOMAS] King Desha,
ruler of the Underworld.
[DESHA laughs]
I will fight you myself.
[DOMAS]
Hmm...
Do not interfere.
[DOMAS] He came here in the
flesh, for a one-on-one fight.
[DOMAS] He thinks he can
face King Bosse... and win?
Oh? You're wondering if I could
really be any match for Bosse,
aren't you?
[giggles]
Not if he were still a giant,
but he bound himself
to the body of a child.
[gasps]
[DOMAS]
How good of a fighter is he?
No... It doesn't matter.
I have to beat him.
[DESHA groans]
[DOMAS gasps]
A lateral swing?
That iron club is far too heavy
to stop with my sword.
If I took the full impact,
my blade would shatter.
I'll let him begin his swing,
strike at the hand,
and disarm him.
Then, I'll land
a clean counterattack.
It appears you're satisfied
with your strategy.
Let's begin.
[DOMAS] Such arrogance.
I'll beat that out of you!
[DESHA]
Heh!
[DOMAS] He's closing
the distance without striking.
[DOMAS]
He still hasn't swung.
What is he planning?
He's getting well
within reach of my blade!
[gasps]
Guh-ah!
This, after you had the nerve
to call me arrogant?
[DOMAS whimpering]
[DESHA snorts]
[laughs]
Observe, men!
He wagered his dignity
to give us this pitiful display!
- Disgraceful! [laughs]
- [DOMAS groaning]
Your rightful place
is at my feet!
[laughs]
Damn... you...
[laughing continues]
Master Domas...
Please, get up!
[DOMAS groaning]
How he trembles,
like a newborn fawn!
A feeble thing with legs
too weak to bear its weight!
- [laughs]
- [DOMAS growling]
[groans]
[DESHA]
Huh?
I commend you for
finding your feet.
[DOMAS]
I already betrayed Prince Bojji.
Even with this indignity,
I could sink no lower.
But at least... I can still
do something for my country.
You're barely able to stand.
What'll you do?
Hold you here.
If only for a moment!
Heh, heh! And for what?
In the end,
you'll accomplish nothing.
You'll only fall
till you can't rise again.
[DESHA]
Do you still mean to oppose me?
- [giggles]
- [growls]
Till my dying breath!
Ugh...
[HOKURO gasps]
[groans]
[ASSASSIN 15A grunts]
Master Domas! I'll fight, too!
I can take at least one with me!
[DOMAS]
Hokuro!
[DESHA grunts]
[gasps]
[growls]
[DESHA]
You need to be stronger.
[wind howling]
[KAGE] From what Mitsumata said,
the gateway to the Underworld
is down at the bottom.
Boy, that's one hell
of a lot of stairs.
We should get moving.
Huh? Something wrong, Gigan?
No, sir.
[KAGE screaming]
Nyeh...
[chuckles]
Ugh. Look, I don't know
what you're expecting.
But do understand,
we're not here to kill anybody.
[gasps]
[DESHA]
I should rephrase that.
We're only here
to kill one person.
Huh? One person?
But... who?
Who is it?
Huh?
[GIGAN grunts]
[roars]
[KNIGHT 15D]
That's Gigan!
[gasps]
Ah.
Is that--? It looks like
the son of old Bosse.
[stammering]
What now?
[sobbing]
[whimpering]
It's him...!
Prince Bojji's here...
He really did survive!
[KAGE]
Huh? Wait a minute.
The Order of the
Underworld is here?
[KAGE]
What?! And so is Desha?!
And some other bozo.
Is that Domas?!
What the hell's
going on in this place?!
[BOJJI whimpering]
Bojji?
[whimpering continues]
[huffing]
[squealing]
[wailing]
[huffing]
I've seen him shaken up before,
but it's never been this bad.
[BOJJI whimpering]
[gasps]
Bojji. Look at me!
It'll be okay.
You've got me here with you.
Right?
[BOJJI whimpers]
[grunting]
[KAGE]
Bojji?!
[huffing]
[groans]
[KAGE]
I can feel it.
All these emotions
are hitting him at once.
I'm sensing things that I've
never felt in him until now.
Painful things.
[KAGE]
Resentment...
Hatred...
The feelings that ruled me,
back before I knew him.
[KAGE]
Hmph!
You did this!
You should be ashamed!
[DOMAS sobbing]
For my betrayal,
I can only atone with my death!
What?!
[KAGE screams]
Master, you can't!
[crack]
[BOJJI gasps]
[HOKURO]
Master Domas!
[HOKURO yelps]
[sighs]
I can't even die!
- [BOJJI sighs]
- What the hell are you doing,
you moron?!
Have you gone insane?!
Hokuro! This overtrained
body is a cruel joke!
I'm so weak...
Master! Get a hold of yourself!
You dying won't
make things better!
Prince Bojji is still alive,
and the only thing
you should worry about
is keeping him safe!
[gasps]
You're absolutely right.
Pathetic! I'm pathetic!
[growls]
I have a duty.
I can't let my feelings
get in the way.
Ah! Right!
[DOMAS growls]
My sword!
Oh. Over there.
Really? This is all
rather farcical.
Men! Seize the fugitive
Gigan immediately!
[KNIGHTS]
Sire!
[yelling]
[roars]
W-Wait, Gigan!
We're not here to fight!
- [GIGAN growls]
- [KNIGHTS screaming]
- [GIGAN grunting]
- [yelling]
- [grunting continues]
- [thudding, crashing]
Ugh. When the Captain's not
around, they're like a gaggle
of unruly children!
[GIGAN snarling]
[GIGAN grunts]
Ah?
[GIGAN growling]
- [BOJJI] Au?!
- [KAGE] Huh?!
Uh?
Come on, Bojji.
You gotta stop them!
- Here!
- [BOJJI] Mm!
Heh, heh! The weakling
has joined the fray!
Can everybody
hang on for a second?!
[BOJJI]
Au-au!
There's no reason
for all this fighting!
[KNIGHTS]
Huh?!
Eh? Eh...
Nyeh.
[GIGAN]
Blaurgh!
[BOTH gasp]
[GIGAN groans]
Gigan!
[BOJJI grunts]
[DESHA chuckles]
Hey, Desha!
I told ya to hang on a second!
[laughs]
And you thought I would listen?
We meet again.
Hail, weakling prince.
[DOMAS]
King Desha!
You said you came here
for one person.
Who is it you seek?
She who released my kingdom's
criminals and conspired
to throw your country
into disarray.
I seek Miranjo.
[DOMAS]
Hmm? Who did he say?
- "Miranjo"?
- I don't know that name.
[DESHA]
Mm! To be so fortunate.
In any case, it's her I want.
[DESHA]
Our accounts will be settled.
Miranjo will pay
her debt with her life.
流されまいと先回りした今日を
nagasaremai to sakimawarishita kyou wo
Tried to stay ahead today to avoid being swept away
昨日が吸い込んだ
kinou ga suikonda
But instead got absorbed by yesterday
ため息　心を後回しにして今日も
tameiki kokoro wo atomawashi ni shite kyou mo
With a sigh, I put my feelings aside for now,
笑う君は飛び込んだ
warau kimi wa tobikonda
and today, as usual, you jump in with a smile
最後ねって決めてたデッドラインを少し延ばした
saigone tte kimeteta deddorain wo sukoshi nobashita
So I pushed back the deadline I'd decided was final
あと一歩で景色が変わるのなら
ato iipo de keshiki ga kawaru nonara
If the view changes after one more step...
何かが変わるのなら
nanika ga kawaru no nara
Maybe something would change...
一番に光れ　笑われても
ichiban ni hikare warawarete mo
Shine brightly with all you've got, even if others may laugh at you,
手を繋いでいるから
te wo tsunaideirukara
because I will be holding your hand
誰かじゃなくて　あなたじゃなくちゃ
dareka janakute anata janakucha
It can't be just someone, it must be you
その涙は救えない
sono namida wa sukuenai
Only you can save those tears
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
あなたに歌ってる　待ってる
anata ni utatteru matteru
I'll be singing for you, waiting for you
この場所で歌ってる　待ってる
kono basho de utatteru matteru
I'll be here, singing and waiting for you