[DOMAS]
King Desha!
You said you came for one
person. Who is it you seek?
She who released my kingdom's
criminals and conspired to throw
your country into disarray.
I seek Miranjo.
Wait, who did he say?
"Miranjo?"
I don't know that name.
[DESHA]
Hee! To be so fortunate.
In any case, it's her I want.
Miranjo will pay
her debt with her life.
Eah-oh...
[KAGE]
What is it, Bojji?
[BOJJI wailing]
[SHIINA]
Miranjo, I beg you!
Anything but him!
[wailing continues]
Leave him be.
Miranjo, he's innocent!
Ah... Eh... ah-oh...
Bojji...
Here, stay safe under Mommy.
I won't let them hurt you.
[SHIINA]
Mm.
Bojji, you have to live!
[arrows whistling]
[sobbing]
[gasps]
- [BOJJI sobs softly]
- [HOKURO gasps]
What's wrong?
[BOJJI sniffling]
Au.
Bojji...
Even now, there is someone choking back tears
誰かが変な涙を 飲み込んで 呑み込んでいる
dareka ga hen na namida wo nomikonde nomikondeiru
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力がこの裏 悪意振り解いて
chikara ga kono ura akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
Look out for these tiny hands
小さなこの手は今
chiisana kono te wa ima
Everything I've fallen in love with
愛してしまった全部全部
aishiteshimatta zenbu zenbu
Including all the curses that have befallen me
降りかかった呪いも全部
furikakatta noroi mo zenbu
All of my feelings for my loved ones
もう愛してしまった想いを全部
mou aishiteshimatta omoi wo zenbu
Give me enough light to protect them
守れるほどの光を
mamoreru hodo no hikari wo
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力が伴う悪意振り解いて
chikara ga tomonau akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
The shadows are closing in, asking, "What are you?"
影は迫る"お前はなんだ"と
kage wa semaru "omae wa nanda" to
Ranking of Kings
Episode 16
Royal Majesty
[DESHA] Hmph. Seems you
don't plan to stop me from
putting down Miranjo,
but I can assure you
Bosse will stand in my way.
The king knows her?
As a matter of fact,
she's one of the people
dearest to his heart.
The bond they share
runs long and deep.
And if Bosse steps up to protect
her, then I must meet him.
[gasps]
[DESHA] Even weakened as he is,
I could only hope to best him.
[DOMAS growls]
Knights of the Order!
Transport Gigan
to the Underworld!
[KAGE, BOJJI gasp]
Weakling. Do you know
you're protecting a criminal
from his due punishment?
- [BOJJI gasps]
- [KAGE] Ah?
[DESHA]
And knowing that...
...do you still
mean to oppose me?
Gigan is a criminal?
But what did he do wrong?
[DESHA]
At one time, he was a warrior.
This was when
I was vying for supremacy
over the Underworld,
against my father.
Gigan was one of the mercenaries
I hired to fight for me.
I believed he would be
a valuable asset.
But I miscalculated.
I hired but one of
the mighty Gigantes,
while my father had raised
an entire army of his kind.
- [GIGANTES CHILD 16A wailing]
- [MERCENARY 16A grunting]
[GIGAN whimpering]
[growling]
[laughter]
Hey, you really think this
is gonna trick those things
into attacking us?
Seems these Gigantes monsters
have a strong instinct
to protect their little ones.
And when they hear
this one crying out,
they'll fly into a rage and
charge in without a real plan.
- [whip cracking]
- [GIGANTES CHILD 16A wailing]
[GIGAN growling]
Huh? Ah!
[GIGANTES bellowing]
[GIGAN growls]
[yelling]
Loose your arrows!
[GIGANTES screaming]
Ah!
[gasps]
[cheering]
[GIGAN grunting]
- [wailing]
- [MERCENARIES laughing]
[GIGAN growling]
Raugh!
[MERCENARIES laughing]
[GIGAN]
Ragh!
[MERCENARIES gasping]
[GIGAN growls]
Kill the traitor!
Gigan has turned against us!
- [GIGAN grunting]
- [MERCENARIES screaming]
Rargh!
[MERCENARY 16A gasps, screams]
[bones cracking,
squishing]
[GIGAN grunting]
[bellows]
[DESHA] We defeated
my father's mercenaries,
but Gigan decimated
our own forces
in the immediate aftermath.
And thus...
...he was branded a criminal.
[GIGANTES CHILD 16A sobbing]
[MERCENARIES laughing]
[slash]
That was all a bit
underwhelming, wasn't it?
To hell with it―
let's get a drink.
[DESHA groans]
[GIGAN growling]
[DESHA] Gigan. I understand
the rage you're feeling.
But... such is life
during times of war!
[roars]
Bojji!
[DESHA]
Ah―
[KAGE]
He just dispelled the lightning!
Sir, did you see that?!
Ah. I did.
[DESHA]
So be it, weakling.
[DESHA groans]
[BOJJI]
Ah.
Au! Au-au, aw-au-au!
Awa-wa, au-au! Au!
Do what? I didn't
pick up one word of that.
[BOJJI]
Au...
[KAGE]
Ah! I'll be right there, Bojji!
'Scuze me, fellas,
comin' through!
[KNIGHTS gasping]
Ah, au!
Yeah, I get it.
You just want me to tell
him you won't fight, right?
[DESHA] Wait. His weapon
is one of Despa's.
That's right. Bojji trained
as Despa's apprentice.
[DESHA]
His apprentice?
But that's not important now.
Bojji didn't jump in
'cause he wanted a fight.
He's only trying to
stop you from taking Gigan.
Please don't make him leave.
We want Gigan to stay with us!
He's Bojji's servant
and my friend!
[GIGAN]
Guh?
[DESHA]
A moment.
Despa.
Do you read me?
[gasps]
I hear you.
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Hmm?
[DESHA] As it happens,
that weakling you trained
has decided to stand in my way.
You met Bojji?
[DESHA]
What exactly did you teach him?
And what is this weapon
you've given him?
Do tell.
I can't afford to waste any
of my strength on this fight.
I have to preserve it for
my showdown with Bosse.
[DESPA]
Mm.
Brother dear. Though it
pains me to say it...
...your full strength would
not suffice against Bojji.
To say nothing of Bosse,
it's no exaggeration
to call his power unmatched.
I can't see what could have kept
him from the top of the ranking,
had he sought it in earnest.
So that's what you make
of the whole situation?
[DESPA] Yes. Oh, and had you
mentioned a plan to overthrow
his kingdom, I would have
advised against it.
Ugh. I wouldn't wish your
obnoxiousness on my worst enemy.
I can't turn away
from this conflict.
I understand that,
but just hear me out.
I think I've devised
a better approach.
[DESHA]
What's that?
We hold off, and send
Bojji to fight Bosse.
[BOJJI, KAGE gasp]
Continue.
Then we move to kill Miranjo
while she's unguarded.
And claim the demon's head.
[DESPA] Hmm. So with your
blessing, the Captain and I
will handle things here in town.
And allow you the
opportunity to withdraw.
Yes. I like that.
Men!
Back to the Underworld!
[KAGE]
Huh?!
Stand aside, weakling.
Gigan is coming with us!
Gigan. You now serve in
the Order of the Underworld.
Huh?!
[BOTH gasp]
[DESPA groaning, retching]
[MERCENARIES laughing, whooping]
[DESPA retches]
[DESHA] If I hope
to defeat our father...
...I need the tactical
prowess and experience
of these mercenaries
to overcome his greater force.
To do other than I did
would have cost their trust,
and this war.
[DESPA grunts]
Perhaps it's what you say,
and your actions
saved our cause.
But our cause can't be just
if we'd sink to the depths
of the man we
would overthrow.
And what you've done here
is beyond despicable!
[gasps]
Did I ask for your approval?!
Shut up! Just shut up!
As you wish.
Enjoy what your
cowardice has won you.
[DESHA growls]
Brother...
I know Despa understands
what you're saying.
He realizes how heavy
the mantle of leadership hangs.
[OUKEN] He sees your heartache,
greater than he or I
will ever have to bear.
And the courage
it took to revolt
against father's brutality.
And I see all that as well,
so I'm happy to play
the role of yes-man.
[MERCENARIES cheering]
[OUKEN growls]
[OUKEN]
And in time...
...I'll give you an army
worthy of your aspirations.
Well disciplined, kind-hearted,
peerless in battle.
The order of knights
I envisioned
will be made a reality!
[OUKEN]
And when it is...
...he'll be counted among them.
Hear this, Gigan. You have
every reason to despise me.
Your forgiveness is not
expected and won't be sought.
[BOTH gasp]
[DESHA]
That said...
This is not an offer,
but an order from your king.
I'd readily take you
back by force.
[gasps]
Gigan.
Do you mean to hide behind
the weakling's sword?
[GIGAN growls]
[gasps]
Ruh...
Uh?
He's saying his heart
is yours, and he says...
"Thanks for everything."
[BOJJI gasps]
[GIGAN whimpers]
Get hold of yourselves.
It's not as if I'm taking him
to be cut up and stewed.
Yeah, fair enough...
Huh?
Ah! Hold on, you guys!
[growling, roaring]
[KAGE]
Ah! Wait! He's not the enemy!
Or at least, not exactly!
[BOJJI whimpers]
[gasps]
[KAGE]
Oh, no!
- [DESHA] Wait.
- [KAGE gasps]
[DESHA]
Let go.
Return to the Underworld!
[UNDERWORLD KNIGHTS]
Sire!
[DESHA]
You lot, as well.
[BOJJI gasps]
The Order of the Underworld
is leaving the castle.
[DOMAS gasps]
[DOMAS, HOKURO grunt]
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[grunts]
Prince Bojji, I have no excuses
to offer for what I've done!
[BOJJI whimpering]
- [DOMAS gasps]
- [KAGE] Hey, sword guy!
You know it won't be that easy!
[DOMAS]
Who are you?
I'm Bojji's buddy
through thick and thin!
You're his friend?
[HOKURO]
Prince Bojji made a real friend.
[KAGE]
Whoa. What's wrong?
[sobbing]
[laughs]
[KAGE]
Ugh. That's really creepy.
I'm just... so happy.
[KAGE]
Huh? Oh, I should mention.
Back when you shoved Bojji
into that big fiery hole,
I was in his bag. I saved him!
[DOMAS gasps]
[DOMAS screams]
Prince Bojji! I'm so sorry!
[KAGE]
Bwah!
Thank you so much,
thank you so much,
thank you so much, stranger!
- Truly, there are no words!
- [sobbing]
[HAKURO, DOMAS sobbing]
Well, y'know...
If you really are sorry,
I suppose I can let it go.
[KAGE]
Bojji!
You think there's any
chance you would be able
to forgive those two?
[wailing]
[whimpers]
[whines]
[KAGE gasps]
You morons! You think
an apology's gonna cut it?!
He has every right to hate you
for the rest of his life
after what the two
of you did to him!
It's just as you say.
[KAGE snarls]
Ya big jerks!
Bojji!
[BOJJI panting]
I get it.
It's hard to forgive
something so awful.
But still...
To see Bojji's heart
all wrapped up in hatred.
I don't want that for him.
I gotta protect him!
Uh? He's already climbed
that high by himself?!
How can you be so cool, Bojji?!
But come to think of it, I'm
pretty quick at climbing, too!
I'll show him and
we can compare notes!
[KAGE] Heck yeah, Bojji,
you're doin' great!
I've always known
you were quick,
but I never realized
you could climb this fast!
I'm gonna head
full speed to the top.
See if you can keep up!
Woo-hoo!
You got this!
[BOJJI sniffles]
Au!
[BOJJI]
[DOMAS]
Hokuro.
I'm sorry to let the blame for
my betrayal fall partly on you.
No need to apologize.
It's fine.
I'm sure if we live good lives,
he'll forgive us in time.
[DOMAS whimpers]
Hokuro!
Let's go!
We'll smash that underworld
portal to bits, right, Master?!
[DOMAS sniffling]
Right. So we shall!
[HOKURO]
Hmph!
[BOJJI, KAGE laughing]
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Prince Despa.
It seems my men's injuries
are nearly all treated.
Well, that's certainly
good to hear.
[CAPTAIN 5A] Once they're ready,
how should we proceed?
[DESPA]
Good question. Um―
[OUKEN wailing]
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[DESPA whimpering]
[gasps]
[OUKEN rasps]
Tried to stay ahead today to avoid being swept away
流されまいと先回りした今日を
nagasaremai to sakimawarishita kyou wo
But instead got absorbed by yesterday
昨日が吸い込んだ
kinou ga suikonda
With a sigh, I put my feelings aside for now,
ため息　心を後回しにして今日も
tameiki kokoro wo atomawashi ni shite kyou mo
and today, as usual, you jump in with a smile
笑う君は飛び込んだ
warau kimi wa tobikonda
So I pushed back the deadline I'd decided was final
最後ねって決めてたデッドラインを少し延ばした
saigone tte kimeteta deddorain wo sukoshi nobashita
If the view changes after one more step...
あと一歩で景色が変わるのなら
ato iipo de keshiki ga kawaru nonara
Maybe something would change...
何かが変わるのなら
nanika ga kawaru no nara
Shine brightly with all you've got, even if others may laugh at you,
一番に光れ　笑われても
ichiban ni hikare warawarete mo
because I will be holding your hand
手を繋いでいるから
te wo tsunaideirukara
It can't be just someone, it must be you
誰かじゃなくて　あなたじゃなくちゃ
dareka janakute anata janakucha
Only you can save those tears
その涙は救えない
sono namida wa sukuenai
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
I'll be singing for you, waiting for you
あなたに歌ってる　待ってる
anata ni utatteru matteru
I'll be here, singing and waiting for you
この場所で歌ってる　待ってる
kono basho de utatteru matteru