[NARRATOR] One of the gods
doomed to extinction, Satun,
once reigned as King
of the Underworld.
He sought to avoid
the fate of his kind,
researching immortality at
the cost of his subjects' lives.
He came to believe that the
secret may lie in the ability
of living beings to
continue their existence
through their offspring.
So he took a human wife
who bore him three sons.
Desha, the eldest,
was a superhuman,
endowed with powers
much like his father's.
The second son, Despa,
was entirely human,
with only a hint of
supernatural ability.
And the youngest, Ouken.
Though possessed
of great physical prowess,
bore no trace of Satun's
godly nature.
[NARRATOR]
In time...
[NARRATOR] ...the three princes
would overthrow and slay
their vicious father, and
the Kingdom of the Underworld
would at last know peace.
[NARRATOR]
But then...
- [OUKEN groans]
- [DESPA, DESHA gasp]
[groaning]
[wails]
[NARRATOR] The immortality that
Satun had long sought manifested
in Ouken, at the age of 25.
I don't want this! You can't let
it take away who I am, Brother!
You have to help me...
I'm begging you!
[sobbing]
[NARRATOR]
And yet...
[OUKEN rasping]
[screams]
[NARRATOR]
Thusly, Ouken was captured...
[NARRATOR] ...and declared
a criminal of the Underworld.
Even now, there is someone choking back tears
誰かが変な涙を 飲み込んで 呑み込んでいる
dareka ga hen na namida wo nomikonde nomikondeiru
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力がこの裏 悪意振り解いて
chikara ga kono ura akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
Look out for these tiny hands
小さなこの手は今
chiisana kono te wa ima
Everything I've fallen in love with
愛してしまった全部全部
aishiteshimatta zenbu zenbu
Including all the curses that have befallen me
降りかかった呪いも全部
furikakatta noroi mo zenbu
All of my feelings for my loved ones
もう愛してしまった想いを全部
mou aishiteshimatta omoi wo zenbu
Give me enough light to protect them
守れるほどの光を
mamoreru hodo no hikari wo
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力が伴う悪意振り解いて
chikara ga tomonau akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
The shadows are closing in, asking, "What are you?"
影は迫る"お前はなんだ"と
kage wa semaru "omae wa nanda" to
Ranking of Kings
Episode 17
The Curse of Immortality
[KAGE] In the end,
I won that race pretty easy.
Au, ah, ah!
No excuses, Bojji.
There's always room
for improvement.
[BOJJI]
Mm!
- Ah!
- Huh?
Ah-ah!
Ah― No fair
takin' a head start!
[BOJJI panting]
[KAGE chuckles]
Woo-hoo!
- Huh?
- [BOJJI] Ah?!
That guy's collapsed!
[KAGE]
Oh, him!
The one who stopped
the fight that time!
Ah, au!
[KAGE] Looks like he's still
alive... but what happened?
Well, whatever it was, we need
to get him to the old biddy.
Au!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Ouken... To me.
[screams]
[VILLAGERS
screaming, whimpering]
He broke his own bones?!
[CAPTAIN 5A]
That's trouble!
[OUKEN]
Hah!
[DESPA, CAPTAIN 5A groan]
[CAPTAIN 5A]
He got us...
It's his Shirasampe!
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Can't move...
[DESPA]
Ouken!
[BOJJI groaning]
[KAGE grunts]
Keep pulling, Bojji!
[APEAS groans]
[KAGE]
Huh?
You okay, spear guy?
What happened?
Ah, au, ah?
Also, what the heck
is going on around here?
Magic beasts and criminals
from the underworld
running around in the castle?
Come to think of it,
did they get you, too?
Hey, Bojji. Is he being quiet
'cause he can't talk either?
[BOJJI]
Au.
Then speak up!
Run away, Prince Bojji.
It's not safe here.
Get out of the castle right
now and don't look back.
What are you talking about?!
[APEAS groans]
Everything's going according
to Lady Miranjo's plan.
Ee-au-oh?
[APEAS] She seeks
the death of Queen Hiling,
and the destruction of
the Kingdom of Bosse.
But why does she want all that?
And the Prince's father,
King Bosse...
...has returned to life
and reclaimed the throne,
in the body of King Daida.
Returned to life?!
[APEAS] He did it to help
fulfill Lady Miranjo's dream.
What is that?
[APEAS] She wants to sit at King
Bosse's side as she once did.
To journey together
with him alone,
unburdened by the troubles
of kingship and family.
That's why she did all this?
[APEAS] In Lady Miranjo's eyes,
her dream is invaluable.
Forgive me, Prince Bojji.
But alas, I can't oppose Lady
Miranjo's wishes even for you.
So you're seriously ready to
kill the old biddy over that?!
[APEAS]
The debt I owe her is greater
than you could ever understand.
Who cares?!
[APEAS]
Then so be it...
I have no choice but to
stop you here, Prince Bojji.
[gasps]
[APEAS grunts]
Prince Bojji...
Can this be...? You've changed.
Yeah, you bet he's changed.
He's way stronger
now than he used to be.
He's literally been
to Hell and back,
and got training from
Despa in the Underworld!
Bojji's no joke!
Despa, eh? It's all
coming together.
[chuckles]
You've started to believe
in yourself in a way
you didn't before, and that
confidence brings you
great power. What's more...
...it seems you've met somebody
with the power to make you
believe in yourself.
[BOJJI gasps]
Mm.
[KAGE]
Hmm?
And that truly is a blessing.
One we both share.
I won't keep you.
Let your heart show
you which path to follow.
Let's go.
[APEAS]
Yes, Prince Bojji...
You've endured such
sadness in your life,
and endured it all alone.
Still, you face the
world with courage,
and you've been a source
of courage for me, as well.
[coughs]
[APEAS] But now, your
strength has grown greater
than I would have
dared to imagine.
Fight on. All hope for
the future of this kingdom
rests upon your shoulders.
[coughs]
Prince Bojji...
Help them...
Lady Miranjo, too...
All these people
whom I hold so dear...
Save them, please...
Do for them what
I never could...
[sobs]
We have arrived, Queen Hiling.
An abandoned guardhouse.
The perfect hideaway.
[HILING gasps]
[squeaking]
[HILING]
Huh...?
[KAGE] I think for starters,
let's beat up those criminals!
Au!
After that, we can go
take care of your old man
and that Miranjo lady!
We'll get this done in a snap!
[BOJJI whimpers]
[BOJJI]
Ah... eh...
No time to second guess
ourselves, bud.
Au!
All right!
- [footsteps]
- [KAGE] Hmm?
[KAGE]
Ouken's back?!
Don't tell me the Captain
and his men got wiped out!
[BOTH yelp]
- [BOJJI] Eh...?
- [KAGE] Huh...?
We've arrived.
That's the portal.
[HOKURO]
It looks like Bojji's friend.
[DOMAS]
The shadow clan.
A tragic people.
Even in death,
they're being used.
[DOMAS]
That child was a rare survivor.
They were exploited,
betrayed, and slaughtered
nearly to the last.
All that's left of them
is their vile reputation,
but from what I've heard,
as a people,
they were pure of heart.
[DOMAS]
Ah. I've got a bad feeling.
Now we've carried out the
promise we made to King Bosse,
let's regroup with Prince Bojji.
Right, good thinking.
[MAGIC MIRROR] What do you
intend to do with me?
[ZOKKU] Well, for the moment,
I'm improvising.
I don't plan on hurting you,
though I would like to know
what you're after here.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
You have no need to know,
but you're free
to do as you wish,
so long as you don't harm me.
And if I do, what happens?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
You die.
[ZOKKU giggles]
Scary stuff!
But the man who was
guarding you is dead now.
If I decide I wanna smash you,
then who do you think
is gonna stop me?
- [MAGIC MIRROR] There you are.
- [ZOKKU gasps]
[screams]
What's this about?
You gonna take her side?
[KAGE]
Wait, Bojji.
[BOJJI]
Au, ah?
Something isn't right here.
Whoa, hold on.
Guy's a monster.
You don't want this fight.
"Monster?" What a joke.
[ZOKKU]
Uh... Are you controlling him?
[MAGIC MIRROR] Beings who lack
reason are easily controlled.
This one is now my servant.
Whoa, is that a talking mirror?
[MAGIC MIRROR chuckles] Shall I
demonstrate by having him
take your life?
Who, me? But why would you?
[MAGIC MIRROR] Due recompense
for taking the life
of one of my favorite students.
Ouken!
What is this? They're
turning on each other?
[ZOKKU growling]
- [ZOKKU grunts]
- Wah!
Gah!
Ah! How awful!
[ZOKKU grunts]
Au!
[KAGE]
Right!
[ZOKKU panting]
[ZOKKU whimpering] You got
a death wish or something?!
Don't think I won't kill a kid!
Ugh!
[ZOKKU]
Are you kiddin'?!
Egads, this one's trouble, too!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Hmm.
Hold on! I surrender!
I give myself completely
to your mercy!
[sobs] I don't think
the fella behind me's got any.
I don't wanna die!
Please don't let him kill me...
- [sobbing]
- Au...
Au...
[chuckles]
[gasps]
What was that?!
[coughing]
[laughs]
Like that?!
Ah... Ha... Wait.
What?
How are you on your feet?
That stuff is deadly!
Why aren't you dead?!
[gasps]
That jerk! What a dirty trick!
[MAGIC MIRROR giggles] But human
poison is nothing to a giant.
[KAGE]
Oh! That's right.
Despa told me
that Bojji's stomach
is almost indestructible.
Wow, he really is the greatest!
[ZOKKU whimpering]
Dammit!
[ZOKKU grunts]
[whimpering]
[BOJJI]
Ah-eh!
[KAGE]
On it!
That little fella's
my best buddy, Bojji,
and my name is Kage.
So who are you?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
One of the shadow clan?
I thought I picked up
the scent of tragedy on you.
Hang on, what's that
s'posed to mean?
Ouken!
[DESPA]
Kage.
No matter what, you mustn't
allow Bojji to confront Ouken!
Even his skill won't
be enough to prevail.
He'll surely be killed!
What exactly could
this mouse be playing at?
[HILING grunts]
Get him, Bojji!
Ouken's got nothin' on you!
[OUKEN rasps]
[BOJJI gasps]
[OUKEN]
Ah... Uh...
Hah!
Ah?
Hah, ah! Ah, hah!
Hah! Hah! Hah!
[KAGE]
Huh?
[OUKEN]
Wah!
[OUKEN gasps]
Au, ah, eh.
Heh!
[OUKEN]
Ah...
Whoa, so he was just throwing
stuff the whole time?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
He's surpassed human ability.
Yeah, you bet he has!
Bojji is awesome―
the best there is!
No one can hold
a candle to my friend!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Really...?
And did you draw
this power out of him?
Who, me? Oh, no way.
It was this guy, Despa.
[MAGIC MIRROR] Hmph.
When a person has somebody who
believes in them,
completely and unreservedly,
it can render them
capable of nearly anything.
[KAGE]
Huh?
[MAGIC MIRROR]
But at other times...
...it renders them vulnerable.
[OUKEN rasps]
[BOJJI]
Hmph!
[OUKEN]
Hah?
[KAGE]
Woo-hoo!
[OUKEN groans]
Huh?! That didn't knock him out?
Bojji! What happened?
Did you miss your shot?!
[BOJJI]
Mm!
[KAGE]
Uh?
[OUKEN]
Wah!
- [OUKEN rasps]
- [BOJJI gasps]
[KAGE]
Not again!
[OUKEN laughs wheezily]
[KAGE] Eh! Did he just
laugh off those hits?!
[MAGIC MIRROR] He's realized
the boy's sword techniques
won't work against him.
Huh? Seriously?
What is his deal?
It's fine.
Bojji still has a special
move up his sleeve.
No way he's ready.
Get him, Bojji!
[MAGIC MIRROR] But against
Ouken, will it be enough?
[OUKEN cackling]
[OUKEN gasps]
There it goes!
This fight is over!
[MAGIC MIRROR chuckles]
[BOJJI gasps]
What the heck did he
do to his sword?!
[OUKEN rasps]
[cackles]
[gasps]
[OUKEN]
Hah!
[OUKEN grunting]
[BOJJI grunting]
Go, Bojji!
Uh... You got this!
[panting]
[MAGIC MIRROR]
He'd best run away.
[gasps] You're right!
Yeah, thanks, mirror!
Bojji!
[MAGIC MIRROR] Why was I...
offering him advice?
That's enough fighting, Bojji!
- You gotta run!
- [BOJJI gasps]
Au!
[KAGE]
Bojji...
[MAGIC MIRROR]
He's grown overconfident
and now he dies
for it. Foolish.
That's not it! Bojji's just...
He's worried.
He thinks everyone will die
if he can't beat Ouken!
Right now, he's not
trying to prove himself,
or even to survive.
He's thinking about everyone
else, the way he always does!
[KAGE]
Don't you get it, jackass?!
[MAGIC MIRROR gasps]
[panting]
[OUKEN]
Ah?
[BOJJI whimpering]
Bojji, you can't!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
What is it?
Bojji's aiming for his vitals.
He's going for a killing blow!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
But Ouken...
...is immortal.
"Immortal"? You mean
there's no way to kill him?!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Indeed, he can't be defeated.
You should inform your friend.
[KAGE]
Oh no!
Bojji! Bojji, over here!
That guy is immortal!
You need to break off
and rest up!
Get up on the castle wall
where he can't reach you!
[BOJJI]
Mm!
[OUKEN]
Ah! Ah!
[BOJJI grunts]
That's it, Bojji!
[OUKEN rasps]
[ZOKKU groans]
Don't let him kill me!
[screams]
Uh?
Bojji!
[OUKEN cackles]
Help! Mirror!
There's gotta be some
way to beat him, right?!
Come to think of it how could
you have known Ouken
was immortal in the first place?
Who are you? You never told me.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
I... am Miranjo.
[KAGE gasps]
You're the one behind all this?
Tried to stay ahead today to avoid being swept away
流されまいと先回りした今日を
nagasaremai to sakimawarishita kyou wo
But instead got absorbed by yesterday
昨日が吸い込んだ
kinou ga suikonda
With a sigh, I put my feelings aside for now,
ため息　心を後回しにして今日も
tameiki kokoro wo atomawashi ni shite kyou mo
and today, as usual, you jump in with a smile
笑う君は飛び込んだ
warau kimi wa tobikonda
So I pushed back the deadline I'd decided was final
最後ねって決めてたデッドラインを少し延ばした
saigone tte kimeteta deddorain wo sukoshi nobashita
If the view changes after one more step...
あと一歩で景色が変わるのなら
ato iipo de keshiki ga kawaru nonara
Maybe something would change...
何かが変わるのなら
nanika ga kawaru no nara
Shine brightly with all you've got, even if others may laugh at you,
一番に光れ　笑われても
ichiban ni hikare warawarete mo
because I will be holding your hand
手を繋いでいるから
te wo tsunaideirukara
It can't be just someone, it must be you
誰かじゃなくて　あなたじゃなくちゃ
dareka janakute anata janakucha
Only you can save those tears
その涙は救えない
sono namida wa sukuenai
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
I'll be singing for you, waiting for you
あなたに歌ってる　待ってる
anata ni utatteru matteru
I'll be here, singing and waiting for you
この場所で歌ってる　待ってる
kono basho de utatteru matteru