[BOJJI]
Yaah!
[BOJJI whimpers]
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Ugh. That was foolish.
[KAGE]
H-Heh...
Hey, Bojji.
[BOJJI gasps]
[KAGE grunts]
[groaning]
Gah!
Even now, there is someone choking back tears
誰かが変な涙を 飲み込んで 呑み込んでいる
dareka ga hen na namida wo nomikonde nomikondeiru
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力がこの裏 悪意振り解いて
chikara ga kono ura akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
Look out for these tiny hands
小さなこの手は今
chiisana kono te wa ima
Everything I've fallen in love with
愛してしまった全部全部
aishiteshimatta zenbu zenbu
Including all the curses that have befallen me
降りかかった呪いも全部
furikakatta noroi mo zenbu
All of my feelings for my loved ones
もう愛してしまった想いを全部
mou aishiteshimatta omoi wo zenbu
Give me enough light to protect them
守れるほどの光を
mamoreru hodo no hikari wo
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力が伴う悪意振り解いて
chikara ga tomonau akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
The shadows are closing in, asking, "What are you?"
影は迫る"お前はなんだ"と
kage wa semaru "omae wa nanda" to
Ranking of Kings
Episode 19
The Last Bastion
[GYAKUZA 19A] The Houma
Kingdom has taken everything
our people had.
They trampled on
our once-rich lands.
They left our fields
blood-soaked and barren!
[CHABI-SHIN]
Hmm...
[CHABI-SHIN] Really?
They look fertile enough.
Or am I wrong?
[gasping]
Ah, well. As you wish.
You have petitioned the gods,
and so we offer you aid.
[GYAKUZA sighing]
Shall we head back home?
[GOD SOLDIER 19A] So we're
going to leave Gyakuza be?
It seems so.
I'd like to make slaves of them.
[CHABI-SHIN] But let them make
pariahs of themselves, for now.
[GOD SOLDIER 19A]
And the Houmas who fled?
[CHABI-SHIN]
Leave them. They're no threat.
Their kingdom is finished.
In any case, the gods need a new
way of ruling over humanity.
The fact Houma's efforts
got them so far is proof.
Their resistance has
completely changed
the relationship between
god and human.
After all, we are hardly
a unified force ourselves.
And humanity's knowledge
grows by leaps and bounds.
The ancient power we wield
has begun to fade away.
The age of the gods is past.
[BEBIN]
What happened to Houma?
To Miranjo and the rest?
[BOSSE panting]
[panting continues]
[whimpering]
[BOSSE whimpering]
[grunts]
[gasps]
You would do...
something this vile...
...and claim it's justified?
[roars]
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[MAN screams]
[crunch]
[GYAKUZA MOTHER]
We were only seeking happiness!
Like all people do!
Please, at least spare my child!
[sobbing]
[BOSSE growling]
Raah!
[crunch, blood splattering]
[BOSSE sobbing]
How awful...
What could drive anyone
to be this cruel?
- [thud]
- [gasps]
[BOSSE]
Take all this and fix her.
My good sir...
[DAIDA (BOSSE)] I decided
I would spend my life
at Miranjo's side from then on.
I wanted nothing but
to see her smile again.
[BEBIN] And of course such a
gruesome experience would change
something within her.
[growls]
It didn't! That wasn't it!
She was betrayed,
maimed, and disfigured.
She suffered terribly.
But I was the one who
kept her from getting better!
And now...
King Bosse, it seems Prince
Bojji needs me at his side.
Wait, that's right.
You sent Bojji off
for training with Despa.
He's grown quite strong
thanks to that.
Can he not win this fight
himself, even so?
No.
As far as the
Mirror's concerned.
Should circumstance demand,
I'll destroy it.
[DAIDA (BOSSE) growls]
[whimpering]
[sobbing]
No. You can't!
- [grunts]
- [sobbing continues]
- [CAPTAIN 5A groaning]
[BOJJI sobbing]
[sobbing stops]
[gasps]
[CAPTAIN 5A]
A-Ah...?
[DESPA groaning]
[DESPA]
Wait! What are you going to do?!
[DESPA gasps]
[gasps]
- [DESPA] Ah―
- [BOJJI] Huh?
[KAGE]
Mama! Mama!
Hey! Can you hear me?
[laughing]
Ae...
[KAGE'S MOTHER]
Kage!
Here I am, Kage! I missed you!
Is that Kage's late mother
on the far shore?
[gasps]
We're in... the realm
between life and death.
Surely, I couldn't
have died, could I?
I've been saving
diligently my whole life!
Was it all for naught?!
[yells]
Will I never have the chance to
spend the nigh-absurd amounts
of wealth I've acquired, Bojji?!
Is fate so cruel?!
[KAGE'S MOTHER]
Hurry and come to Mama, Kage!
Coming!
[DESPA sobbing]
[KAGE humming]
Oh, no! Kage's crossing
to the land of the dead!
[gasps]
[DESPA]
You must turn back, Kage!
- [BOJJI] Au-au! Au!
- [DESPA] Kage!
[gasps]
Can he not hear us?
Au...
- Ha--!
- [gasps]
Now I see.
We're able to observe this
world, but we're not part of it.
And that would mean... we're
trapped in somebody else's mind.
[gasps]
[DESPA]
The mind of Miranjo!
- Ah-eh! Ah-eh!
- We're still alive.
I've long had a theory,
but this is proof that
I'm too good-looking to die.
Which is clearly
beside the point!
- Ah! Kage!
- [KAGE] Mama!
[DESPA]
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
You're almost here, Kage!
Come back! Don't do it, Kage!
Ah-eh!
[KAGE]
Mama!
Mm?
Hmm?
If you cross to the other shore,
you'll never be able to get back
to this side.
- Miranjo!
- Ee-ah-oh...
Who the heck are you, lady?
Have you severed all
attachments to this life?
Severed all... attachments?
Come on, Kage!
[KAGE]
Hmm?
Hurry. Just a little further!
Wait, Mama...
[gasps]
Bojji...
Ah-eh!
[KAGE]
Bo... jji.
Bojji. Bojji. Bojji.
Bojji. Bojji.
Bojji!
[whimpers]
You can do it...
It's okay, Kage...
Come be with Mama again...
Please!
[KAGE]
Mama... I...
I wanna help Bojji...
[KAGE'S MOTHER whimpers]
[sobbing]
[KAGE]
Mama!
How ya been over there?
Is it nice on that side?
[KAGE'S MOTHER whimpers]
Yes! It's wonderful!
I have nothing
to complain about!
And I'm in good company, too.
[KAGE]
Glad to hear it.
Mama... I've got things to take
care of on the other side.
I can't join you just yet.
[KAGE'S MOTHER]
Ah...
Right...
Right.
Then you go back there
and get 'em done!
Got it! And I swear I'll
be right back here after that!
Keep a good eye out,
'cause I might be an old man
by the time you see me again!
[KAGE'S MOTHER sobs]
I'll be right here...
Bye!
[inaudible]
Please, give me a better look
at your face before you go...
[sobbing]
My sweet boy...
Do your best out there!
[sobbing]
[KAGE]
Hmph!
For now you remain
among the living,
but you've saved nothing yet.
[KAGE]
Hmph. I recognize that voice.
You're Miranjo, right?
Why'd you pull me back across?
Well, even if you don't wanna
explain, you have my thanks!
Except, you prob'ly shouldn't,
seeing as how this is all
pretty much your fault.
[MIRANJO]
Hmph.
Nah, it's fine. Thanks, Miranjo!
[gasps]
[KAGE]
Hang on, Bojji! I'm on my way!
[gasps]
[grunts]
Miranjo!
[DAIDA]
Ah...
My face...
[DAIDA]
Mm-hmm! Everything's healed!
It is!
- [sobbing]
- [laughing]
Ah!
Wait. What's this?
I've been saved. Thanks so much!
- [DAIDA gasps]
- And goodbye.
What? But I'll be
all alone again!
Don't leave me!
Please!
[MIRANJO]
It'll be okay.
[DAIDA gasps]
[MIRANJO]
And soon...
And soon, what?
What else is going
to happen to me?
[gasps]
[MITSUMATA]
They're mortally wounded,
and Queen Hiling
has no power left.
There's no saving them.
[stomach growls]
[MITSUMATA gasps]
[MITSUMATA]
Gah!
[OUKEN slurping]
[MITSUMATA groaning, rasping]
[OUKEN sighs]
[MITSUMATA]
Please... Someone!
Keep your damned filthy
hands off him, you cur!
Master Bebin!
I'm here.
[DORSHE huffing]
What's that?!
It seems he's immortal.
[DOMAS]
You mean...
All we can do is constrict
his movement enough
that he's unable to resist.
Sounds fun.
[knuckles cracking]
[gasps]
[APEAS]
Lady Miranjo...?
She's gone. Where is she?
Prince Bojji's injured. I can't
get the bleeding to slow down.
We don't have long.
We need Queen Hiling's power!
That power's been exhausted.
Her Majesty can't help.
Does that mean... all is lost?
[DORSHE]
No. Not yet.
[gasps]
Dorshe's right. There's one more
person who can save their lives.
Yes. E-Except...
For now, we must
hold out against him.
Please allow me
the honor, gentlemen.
[BEBIN]
Easy, Domas. Stay on your toes.
[DOMAS]
I know.
[DOMAS] Prince Bojji, you've
grown terrifyingly powerful.
I couldn't hope to stand
against you myself, now.
[DOMAS] And still, my opponent
was able to bring you down.
Though, perhaps your
needle-sword is ill-suited
to battling an immortal, however
strong the hand may be
that wields it.
May that slender blade
soon welcome mine
back into your service.
[OUKEN rasps]
[bellows]
He must be powerful
to strike with such abandon.
Fine, then! I'll
shatter your sword!
[grunting]
[DOMAS growls]
[DOMAS]
What the hell was that?
No matter, I'm clearly
the better swordsman here.
[snarls]
[gasps]
[bellows]
- [OUKEN] Hah!
- [DOMAS grunts]
[whimpering]
What's going on?!
[DOMAS growling]
Bebin, what is this?
[BEBIN] He shouts as a feint,
then hits you in a vital point
with a foreign object
to paralyze you, like so.
And you can't break his sword,
thanks to his immortal blood.
It sounds like
you knew all this.
Were you planning to tell me?
[BEBIN] I thought it best
to let you see for yourself.
You, and our friends
waiting to join the fray.
[sighs]
Well, let's get to it, shall we?
[APEAS]
Right!
[DORSHE snarls]
[DOMAS bellows]
[OUKEN]
Rah!
[OUKEN laughs wheezily]
On your right!
[OUKEN rasps]
[DORSHE grunts]
Nice breeze today.
[snarls]
[DORSHE grunts]
It shocks me, how much
abuse you can endure.
If only he'd bother
learning how to use a blade.
You lout.
Hey, give it a rest!
[grunting]
He's shut down.
That's why they're the Big Four.
[panting]
[DORSHE grunts]
[OUKEN rasping]
So, what are we doing with him
now that I have him pinned down?
[DESPA] Be still a moment.
Feel your opponent's rhythm.
Let yourself fall into the flow.
Your opponent
dictates it for now...
...but persevere.
[DESPA]
Your training won't betray you.
At the precipice of defeat,
its worth will be revealed.
That precipice is where
you can reverse the tide...
...Ouken.
[OUKEN gasps]
[DORSHE grunts]
Ah!
[DESPA] At that point...
lies a new energy.
Seize that sensation, Ouken,
Sword King of the Underworld.
He seems to have
gone into a daze.
[BEBIN grunts]
[gasps]
- [OUKEN] Hah!
- What?!
Gah!
[OUKEN]
Hah!
[coughs]
[DORSHE]
Over here!
[BOTH yell]
[groaning]
[DORSHE growls]
[BEBIN grunting]
[gasps]
This battle's not over yet.
Yes.
We're still standing.
We're the Big Four.
[ALL]
The last bastion of the kingdom!
Tried to stay ahead today to avoid being swept away
流されまいと先回りした今日を
nagasaremai to sakimawarishita kyou wo
But instead got absorbed by yesterday
昨日が吸い込んだ
kinou ga suikonda
With a sigh, I put my feelings aside for now,
ため息　心を後回しにして今日も
tameiki kokoro wo atomawashi ni shite kyou mo
and today, as usual, you jump in with a smile
笑う君は飛び込んだ
warau kimi wa tobikonda
So I pushed back the deadline I'd decided was final
最後ねって決めてたデッドラインを少し延ばした
saigone tte kimeteta deddorain wo sukoshi nobashita
If the view changes after one more step...
あと一歩で景色が変わるのなら
ato iipo de keshiki ga kawaru nonara
Maybe something would change...
何かが変わるのなら
nanika ga kawaru no nara
Shine brightly with all you've got, even if others may laugh at you,
一番に光れ　笑われても
ichiban ni hikare warawarete mo
because I will be holding your hand
手を繋いでいるから
te wo tsunaideirukara
It can't be just someone, it must be you
誰かじゃなくて　あなたじゃなくちゃ
dareka janakute anata janakucha
Only you can save those tears
その涙は救えない
sono namida wa sukuenai
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
I'll be singing for you, waiting for you
あなたに歌ってる　待ってる
anata ni utatteru matteru
I'll be here, singing and waiting for you
この場所で歌ってる　待ってる
kono basho de utatteru matteru