[SHIINA]
Mm.
[SHIINA] Small though it may be,
this is our country.
And, Bojji, it will
be yours in time.
[BOJJI whimpering]
Ah! Ah!
[sobbing]
[DESPA] Bojji. Is that your
mother standing on
the far shore?
She looks like a strong lady.
[sniffles]
[DESPA] And that must be
Miranjo's mother at her side.
But in light of
present circumstances...
...I can't imagine this
will be a happy reunion.
Even now, there is someone choking back tears
誰かが変な涙を 飲み込んで 呑み込んでいる
dareka ga hen na namida wo nomikonde nomikondeiru
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力がこの裏 悪意振り解いて
chikara ga kono ura akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
Look out for these tiny hands
小さなこの手は今
chiisana kono te wa ima
Everything I've fallen in love with
愛してしまった全部全部
aishiteshimatta zenbu zenbu
Including all the curses that have befallen me
降りかかった呪いも全部
furikakatta noroi mo zenbu
All of my feelings for my loved ones
もう愛してしまった想いを全部
mou aishiteshimatta omoi wo zenbu
Give me enough light to protect them
守れるほどの光を
mamoreru hodo no hikari wo
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力が伴う悪意振り解いて
chikara ga tomonau akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
The shadows are closing in, asking, "What are you?"
影は迫る"お前はなんだ"と
kage wa semaru "omae wa nanda" to
Ranking of Kings
Episode 20
Immortal vs. Invincible
Miranjo...
Hello, Mother.
And you as well, Queen Shiina.
Huh. Forgive me
if I'm a bit brisk...
[knuckles cracking]
...but I am face to face
with my own killer.
[gasps]
I hope you don't plan
on returning the favor.
You know there's no coming
back to this shore.
My bad habit of cracking
my knuckles outlived me.
I have no need to threaten you.
[MIRANJO] Then has my mother
recruited you to come here
and try to steer me from
my chosen course?
Or did you join her hoping to
witness a display of penitence?
[laughs] You've got a mouth on
you, you insufferable little―
[MIRANJO'S MOTHER]
Tell me!
Miranjo... Why would
you do all this?
I see... You couldn't cross
if you wanted to, could you?
[gasps]
[growls]
[coughs]
This can't be where I die...
[whimpers]
Please...
I shall move your soul into the mirror.
[DEMON 3A] Lessev sluos ru
oyeb llahs rorrim eht.
However, when you actually do die,
Slatrom fomla ereht
gnitra ped nodna.
I shall devour your soul.
Em deyar tebec iwt gni vah ro
fes nep mocere udsa.
This is twice now,
that you have betrayed me.
Ruoved ot enim
emoceb llahs luos taht.
[SHIINA]
Will you carry on as you have?
All the death and misery
you've wrought...
It's a lonesome and treacherous
path you've chosen to walk.
And when you
stumble on that path,
- who will be left to catch you?
- [gasps]
[SHIINA]
What a pitiful child.
You've sacrificed so much,
and this is what's left of you.
That's all you have to say?!
[SHIINA] Hmph. My resentment
has long since faded.
[gasps]
[growls]
[SHIINA]
I've heard your story.
We ought to despise evil deeds,
but not those who commit them.
My son grew up
strong, didn't he?
Not even you could kill him.
And there are many who would
protect him with their lives.
- Can you say the same?
- [MIRANJO whimpering]
Miranjo! What you're doing
won't make you happy.
It's only going to
bring you more suffering!
[MIRANJO gasps]
You're wrong...
I know that's not true!
I'll win, and I'll get
to be with King Bosse!
And we'll be happy together
like we used to be!
Oh, darling...
[BOTH gasp]
[MIRANJO sobbing]
I can't go back...
Don't tell me to give up!
[BOJJI]
Ah, ah!
This wind is going to sweep us
away back to the living world!
[MIRANJO sobbing]
[MIRANJO] King Bosse is
the only thing I have left...
[sobbing]
I've got nothing else...
Nothing...
[DESPA] Bojji, the one to put
a stop to Miranjo's plot
will be you.
When your mother's killer
is at last brought to heel,
you will pass judgment.
Can you kill her?
[BOJJI grunting]
Ah, au-au!
Time and again, you prove
yourself to be the boy
I believed you to be.
[DESPA]
Inside her mind,
I was able to glean some
of her memories.
I'll show you.
That way, you'll be better
equipped to decide her fate.
[BOJJI gasps]
A sad tale, indeed.
I struggled mightily
to hold back tears myself.
Au... Au-au...
[sobs]
True.
However, it pains me
to say she's beyond
salvation at this point.
[BOJJI gasps]
[rasping]
[panting]
[huffing]
[APEAS groaning]
[gasps]
- [DORSHE grunts]
- [DOMAS gasps]
[GROUP groaning]
[APEAS groans]
Damn it...
[HOKURO wheezing]
[DOMAS]
Hokuro!
Look! I finally got
a shot in, Master Domas―
[grunts]
Not like this...
[MIRANJO] At some point, I
stopped feeling anything at all.
Could something have
changed when I broke my promise
to the demon?
King Bosse began
achieving his dreams,
at the cost of those around him.
I began to manipulate others
in pursuit of my own ends,
without remorse or regret.
[MIRANJO]
Until...
...the sensation I'd lost
suddenly returned to me.
[OUKEN rasps]
[MAGIC MIRROR] Could this...
really be what I wanted?
[whimpering]
Is that...?
[MIRANJO] My only salvation
is you, King Bosse.
Miran...
[MIRANJO gasps]
King Bosse...?
Then you've already passed on.
[DAIDA gasps]
[MAGIC MIRROR] I will use
Prince Daida to bring King Bosse
back to life.
[gasps]
Miranjo...
You're... the Mirror?
[DAIDA whimpering]
For so long...
...I wanted to know what kind
of woman you really were.
Miranjo...
I know... I could have...!
[gasps]
[groans]
My wound is still open!
I'm going to bleed out, and
Bojji and Kage are dying, too!
[KAGE]
Bojji!
[gasps]
That's right. I remember.
Here, Kage... Everybody is
moments away from succumbing
to blood loss
if nothing is done.
[KAGE]
Wha-What do I do?
Above all else, you must
stay out of Ouken's sight.
Get the captain.
[KAGE]
Why him?
[DESPA] He knows a technique
that can stop bleeding.
The Captain is our
last hope for survival.
Bojji, I swear I'll get
you out of this alive!
Huh?
[KAGE] But wait...
My wounds are healed.
Was it her?
[MAGIC MIRROR whimpering]
[CAPTAIN 5A]
I stopped the bleeding.
When he approaches,
I'll grab his blade!
- [CAPTAIN 5A] Gah!
- Captain!
Oh no, he saw me!
- Huh?!
- [BOJJI grunts]
[KAGE]
Stop! You're too hurt!
[BOJJI grunts]
[MAGIC MIRROR]
King Bosse...
[DESPA]
No!
Are you the old crackpot
who stole his own son's body?
What's your deal?
[huffing]
[grunts]
- Ah!
- Bojji!
[KAGE growls]
- You bastard!
- Don't, Kage!
[growling]
[thudding]
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
How fortunate that none of you
have to die alone.
[ALL groaning]
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
Don't bother.
[hisses]
[DESPA groans]
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
You're Despa, aren't you?
I appreciate you
looking after Bojji.
[DESPA]
Brother, call down the―
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
It won't help.
Lightning poses no threat to me.
Rather, no attack
is a threat to me.
However...
You understand.
[DESPA grunts]
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
Hmm.
[groaning]
[KAGE]
I know that light!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
King Bosse...
[gasping]
Daida?
What's going on?
Get back here, Hiling!
[panting]
[gasping]
[gasps]
Our wounds are...
totally healed.
[BEBIN] Could King Daida
have saved us all
with the healing magic he
inherited from Queen Hiling?
Has King Bosse
come back to our side?
[KAGE]
Bojji! [sobs]
Au!
Are you absolutely sure
you're not gonna die?!
[BOJJI]
Hmm!
[grunting]
Ho!
[KAGE]
Whoo!
He's back! Bojji! Bojji!
Bojji!
I couldn't have imagined Prince
Bojji had this much energy!
[HOKURO whimpering]
And Despa is back!
And the Captain!
[GROUP laughing]
I almost forgot.
We haven't dealt
with that guy yet!
Huh? Bojji!
[huffing]
[DOMAS]
I knew it. King Bosse!
[panting continues]
[BOJJI]
Huh?
Listen, Bojji. You've made
a valiant effort against Ouken,
but now, there's nothing
left to do but stand aside.
You are not defeated!
Knowing when to
entrust others with a task
is valuable in itself.
[BOJJI]
Mm.
Let him take care of it.
[DESPA] Ideally, they'll
take care of each other.
After all, we still don't
know his true aim.
[DOMAS] Immortal or not,
he faces the great King Bosse.
[DESPA] In the worst
case scenario, we wait
and strike both of
them with one bolt.
[sighs]
[DAIDA (BOSSE)] That power
is more taxing than I realized.
I can barely muster
half of my strength now.
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
She's quite the woman.
- [grass rustling]
- Hmm?
Au-awa.
Thanks for fixin' everybody up!
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
Bojji...
Such a kind and honest boy.
[KAGE] Hey! Not that you don't
seem freakishly strong,
but be careful.
That guy is immortal!
Oh, and good to meet ya.
Um, I'm Bojji's best buddy!
- [gasps]
- I see.
- Au-ah!
- [KAGE laughs]
[DESPA] Right, then.
A-A moment, gentlemen!
What the heck's
got you so spooked?
[whispering]
We can't know for certain that
he's on our side yet.
He could be dangerous!
Rather, we know him to be
the mastermind behind this.
Our true enemy.
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
So you're the one who overcame
even my son's vast power.
It's been so long since
I felt such a thrill.
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
What an absurd notion.
If only you had
any skill to speak of,
perhaps that feeling would
last a minute or two.
- Watch out!
- [clang]
[OUKEN]
Ah?
You really thought you
could strike me down with
a simple piece of steel?
[KAGE]
Ah! He's a monster!
It's over, and we've won!
[DESPA]
The power of a giant,
condensed into
the body of a boy.
He must be unimaginably tough!
The power of immortality will
fall... to our invincible king!
"Invincible"?
[KAGE]
Hmph!
[clanging]
[OUKEN rasps]
Bojji, we lose if Ouken
manages to beat your dad.
Flipside? If your dad comes out
of this fight on top...
...you can definitely beat
the scheming old jerk,
and then we win!
[gasps]
[DAIDA (BOSSE) growls]
[OUKEN]
Ah―
BOTH gasp]
[DAIDA (BOSSE) grunts]
[CAPTAIN 5A gasps]
He's swinging that club
faster than we can see!
Even that didn't
put him down for good.
Are you ready to
take up the burden
of everyone's misery, Ouken?
[OUKEN rasping]
It could be that
you're too far gone.
Salvation might be
out of reach for you.
[squelching]
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
Hmm.
Wait, what the heck
is he gonna do now?
[BOJJI]
Au...
Ouken is gonna keep recovering!
You gotta watch your back!
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
Hmm.
I think I get it!
He's gonna keep him pinned down
under that chunk of dirt!
[OUKEN]
Ah... A-Ah... Ah―
[armor pieces clanking]
[squelching]
Hey, that's not gonna
work any better than it did
the first time! Don't you have
an actual plan to beat him?!
[OUKEN rasping]
[OUKEN screeching]
[BOJJI gasps]
- He... He sealed him inside!
- [OUKEN screeching]
- He really did it...
[DESPA whimpers]
[screeching continues]
[muffled screeching]
He's the scariest thing here!
[DORSHE]
King Bosse...
[gasping]
[BOJJI]
Ah...
[KAGE]
Huh?
Wait a sec. Bojji!
Forget what I said!
Don't fight him!
Au, au!
It's definitely not okay!
Tried to stay ahead today to avoid being swept away
流されまいと先回りした今日を
nagasaremai to sakimawarishita kyou wo
But instead got absorbed by yesterday
昨日が吸い込んだ
kinou ga suikonda
With a sigh, I put my feelings aside for now,
ため息　心を後回しにして今日も
tameiki kokoro wo atomawashi ni shite kyou mo
and today, as usual, you jump in with a smile
笑う君は飛び込んだ
warau kimi wa tobikonda
So I pushed back the deadline I'd decided was final
最後ねって決めてたデッドラインを少し延ばした
saigone tte kimeteta deddorain wo sukoshi nobashita
If the view changes after one more step...
あと一歩で景色が変わるのなら
ato iipo de keshiki ga kawaru nonara
Maybe something would change...
何かが変わるのなら
nanika ga kawaru no nara
Shine brightly with all you've got, even if others may laugh at you,
一番に光れ　笑われても
ichiban ni hikare warawarete mo
because I will be holding your hand
手を繋いでいるから
te wo tsunaideirukara
It can't be just someone, it must be you
誰かじゃなくて　あなたじゃなくちゃ
dareka janakute anata janakucha
Only you can save those tears
その涙は救えない
sono namida wa sukuenai
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
I'll be singing for you, waiting for you
あなたに歌ってる　待ってる
anata ni utatteru matteru
I'll be here, singing and waiting for you
この場所で歌ってる　待ってる
kono basho de utatteru matteru