[gasps]
[BOJJI]
Ah?
Huh?
[ALL gasping]
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
I'm sorry to keep you, Miranjo.
I could hear your voice
crying out in pain.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
King Bosse, I've...
I've done some things
that can't be taken back.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
The love between us...
The life we'd shared...
It should have
been enough for me.
But I...
[MIRANJO] A giantess
can only bear one child,
and the end of King Bosse's
life is approaching.
I can't let him pass on,
not without another child.
[MIRANJO]
While King Bosse is away,
I'll call in a hostile nation to
attack the castle, and then...
...using Prince Bojji as bait...
[MIRANJO]
...I will kill Queen Shiina.
[DAIDA (BOSSE)] So, you set
the stage for Daida to be born
as the vessel for
my resurrection.
[MAGIC MIRROR] Queen Hiling will
not accept the loss of her son.
Her pain will be immense, and
she's sure to struggle mightily.
For her own sake,
we should offer her a quick end.
[MAGIC MIRROR sobbing]
I'm so sorry...
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
I see.
You've found
your true self again.
Your feelings for me
drove you to this.
The fault is mine for
placing my burdens on you
with no way to carry them.
[DAIDA (BOSSE)] Miranjo, I'm
sorry, but all your suffering
will have been in vain.
[MAGIC MIRROR gasps]
Are you saying...?
[DAIDA (BOSSE)] Know this:
if I fall here, I will join you.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Yes, you surely would.
But you can't...
Forgive me...
Even now, there is someone choking back tears
誰かが変な涙を 飲み込んで 呑み込んでいる
dareka ga hen na namida wo nomikonde nomikondeiru
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力がこの裏 悪意振り解いて
chikara ga kono ura akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
Look out for these tiny hands
小さなこの手は今
chiisana kono te wa ima
Everything I've fallen in love with
愛してしまった全部全部
aishiteshimatta zenbu zenbu
Including all the curses that have befallen me
降りかかった呪いも全部
furikakatta noroi mo zenbu
All of my feelings for my loved ones
もう愛してしまった想いを全部
mou aishiteshimatta omoi wo zenbu
Give me enough light to protect them
守れるほどの光を
mamoreru hodo no hikari wo
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力が伴う悪意振り解いて
chikara ga tomonau akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
The shadows are closing in, asking, "What are you?"
影は迫る"お前はなんだ"と
kage wa semaru "omae wa nanda" to
Ranking of Kings
Episode 21
The Swordsmanship of a King
I am your king,
and I'll brook no attempt
to steal back Daida's body.
Accept this.
Those who renew their allegiance
shall be allowed to continue
in my service.
And those who refuse...
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
...shall die here!
[KAGE whimpers]
King Bosse...
Don't do this.
[BOJJI]
Kuh...
[BOJJI gasps]
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
Make your choice!
Pledge your lives
to me once more,
or throw them away
in Daida's name!
These are the only
paths before you!
[inaudible]
[BOJJI]
Mm.
[HILING panting]
[KAGE]
Don't, Bojji!
If you fight that guy,
you'll― Huh?
[BOJJI]
Mm.
[KAGE gasps]
Yeah, you're right.
Our hearts are one now!
This is the only right way
for things to end.
If we die here, we die together!
Ah. Au!
[KAGE]
Yeah!
[BOJJI]
Mm.
So be it.
Which side are
the rest of you on?
[gasping]
I'm with the prince!
[KAGE]
Huh?
[HOKURO]
Master Domas...
[DOMAS] I'll take...
the path of righteousness!
You already know!
It was never in doubt.
Your Majesty...
Y-You willed the throne to
Prince Bojji upon your death.
And we of the Big Four...
...serve the rightful king!
[KAGE]
Woo-hoo!
Look at that, Bojji!
Everyone's on your team!
[sniffles]
[DAIDA (BOSSE) chuckles]
Then you choose death!
[growling]
[BOJJI gasping]
[gasping]
Prince Bojji!
[BEBIN]
Stand down!
Let us protect you!
We'll gladly lay down our lives!
[DESPA]
Sorry to say it, gentlemen,
but even your considerable
abilities are of no use here.
For all your noble sentiment,
your deaths would do naught
but fatten the worms.
[gasping]
[groaning]
That may well be the case, but I
vowed to protect Prince Bojji!
This is the least I can do
to atone for my sins!
I genuinely admire
your dedication, Domas...
But alas...
Now, Bojji!
Haah...!
- [clang]
- [groans]
[gasps]
Au?!
[gasping]
[APEAS]
Did Prince Bojji kill him?!
[DESPA]
Heavens, no!
Bojji is a most
merciful swordsman.
[DORSHE]
Merciful?
[DESPA] Which is to say, his is
the swordsmanship of a king
who's rejected killing!
[gasping]
[KAGE groaning]
[BOJJI gasps]
Ya gotta be more careful.
Au, ah-ah.
And furthermore, his mentor
stands among you even now!
That being me!
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
It's over.
The outcome is not in question.
I won't be defeated
by Bojji's sword.
All I can do
is finish him quickly.
[DORSHE]
If it comes to it...
[APEAS]
No matter the cost...
[BEBIN]
Mitsumata...
Prince Bojji
must leave here alive.
[DESPA] I'm so sorry, Bojji,
but even if you see
King Bosse's attack coming,
it's not likely
you'll be able to dodge it.
Could your potential
offer some shred of hope?
No.
There's none.
I trained you in
pursuit of my own ends.
Once again...
I've failed as a teacher.
[KAGE]
Bojji...
Everything you've done,
from the moment we met...
...all of it...
...was to help others.
[gasps]
[BOSSE growls]
[BOSSE snarling]
[APEAS]
Prince Bojji!
- [clang]
- [gasps]
[BOSSE grunts]
[BOSSE snarls]
[KAGE gasps]
[BOJJI panting]
[grunts]
Ah, ah!
Hah!
[KAGE]
Bojji!
[BOSSE snarls]
[gasps]
[BOJJI]
Hmm!
Ah!
[BOSSE growling]
[BOSSE snarls]
Ah―
Tch!
[BOJJI snarls]
[BOSSE gasps]
[DAIDA (BOSSE) groaning]
[BOSSE]
Gah!
Then it's true...
You really have...
D-ah!
[gasping]
[DOMAS gasps]
[DOMAS]
Prince Bojji.
This is not
the swordsmanship of a king.
[DOMAS whimpers]
[KAGE]
Bojji...
Bojji!
[DESPA gasps]
[chuckles]
[DESPA]
This... is the swordsmanship...
...of a king!
[DAIDA (BOSSE) groaning]
[BOJJI]
Mm!
[DAIDA (BOSSE) groaning]
[BEBIN]
The invincible King Bosse...
[DORSHE] ...is utterly helpless
against Prince Bojji.
[gasps]
[groans]
[growls]
[snarls]
[DESPA]
If he keeps this up, he'll die.
[wheezing]
[groaning]
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
What are... these feelings?
Uncertainty...
Guilt...
Affection...
And...
Happiness...
[DAIDA (BOSSE)]
Tch!
[coughing]
[groaning]
[huffing]
I'm sorry I didn't do more...
Forgive me...
[MAGIC MIRROR]
I see now...
When I brought you back to life,
it wasn't for your sake...
[gasps]
[MIRANJO] I woke you from your
rest... out of selfish desire.
[gasps]
Ah!
Go for it!
[MIRANJO gasps]
- [DAIDA (BOSSE) groans]
- [MIRANJO gasps]
[groaning]
[JUDGE 4A] Would you really
decline the first-place ranking,
even knowing the divine
treasure vault may offer
the means to save Prince Ouken?
[DESHA]
Ugh.
Does that mean you believe
what Prince Despa has told you?
[DESHA] He's a weakling
and a buffoon, but no liar.
If Despa says he can lift the
curse of immortality from Ouken,
then I'm sure he can.
[JUDGE 4A growls]
[DESHA]
Ugh. How obnoxious.
Phoo.
[DAIDA (BOSSE) whimpering]
This body...
I have to return it...
to Daida...
It's not mine to destroy...
[MAGIC MIRROR]
King Bosse, if I'd realized
how I was making you suffer.
[gasps]
No... Miranjo!
I'm to blame for
everybody's suffering!
In my life, I'd been
blessed with all the joy
this world could offer.
And yet... all it
would offer you was me.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Prince Bojji...
I implore you...
Destroy me.
[DAIDA (BOSSE) gasps]
No, Miranjo!
[MAGIC MIRROR]
The curse will be lifted,
and King Daida will return.
[CAPTAIN 5A gasps]
[whimpering]
[MAGIC MIRROR]
To be a king,
this is the burden
you must bear.
It's your choice to make
and to carry out.
[DAIDA (BOSSE) sobbing]
Miranjo, all I wanted...
...was for you to be happy.
We owe much to those we rule,
and we should embody the spirit
we would foster in their hearts.
So train diligently,
son of mine.
You can't do that!
Please, spare her life,
Prince Bojji!
Lady Miranjo! Quick,
turn yourself to diamond!
[MAGIC MIRROR sighs] I don't
have nearly enough magic left.
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[DESPA]
Because she...
[DAIDA (BOSSE) groaning]
Miranjo... now we
can go together...
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Yes... King Bosse!
[APEAS sobbing]
Ah!
[KAGE wailing]
Stop it! Call him back!
Don't make him do it!
I won't. This must be
settled here!
Listen, Kage.
Miranjo herself seeks closure,
and her deliverance has
to come by Bojji's hand.
In your words, this is the only
right way for things to end!
[KAGE sobs]
Bojji...
[DESPA]
And when it's done,
I can find a way to
save my brother.
Prince Bojji...
[DAIDA (BOSSE) gasps]
[BOJJI]
Hmm.
Ah, au.
[MAGIC MIRROR]
Save me... from the demon?
[sobs]
Prince Bojji...
Forgive me, and...
...thank you.
[APEAS wheezes]
[sobs]
- [DEMON 3A] Hmm.
- [BOJJI gasps]
- [gasping]
- [DEMON 3A laughing]
There he is! Captain!
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Right!
[DEMON 3A chuckles]
Boba!
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Raugh!
[DESPA gasps]
[DEMON 3A]
Boba bo. Babbaa!
Miranjo! What's going on?!
King Bosse, I'm sorry. I lied.
I won't be able
to join you in death.
A vow made to a demon
must never be broken.
What is this...?
How can fate be this cruel?
Why should you be the only one
to endure such misery?
[DEMON 3A]
Heh...
[MIRANJO] Thank you King
Bosse... for all you've done...
Don't take her, please!
Let her go...
Daida... You have to...
[KAGE gasps]
Bojji!
Ah!
[gasps]
[KAGE]
Huh?
[MIRANJO sobbing]
So you've finally arrived.
[MIRANJO gasps]
Hey! What are you eating?
[DEMON 3A gasps]
My name is Miranjo!
What's your name?
[DEMON 3A whimpering]
[MIRANJO groans]
He ran off somewhere.
[MIRANJO sobbing]
[MIRANJO gasps]
I'm sorry!
I know I broke
my promise to you!
[SOULS screaming]
[MIRANJO gasps]
[screaming continues]
[DEMON 3A growling, slurping]
[gasps]
[SOULS screaming]
[SOULS groaning, screaming]
[SOUL 21B shrieking]
[MIRANJO whimpering]
[DEMON 3A]
Welcome...
[MIRANJO gasps]
[DEMON 3A]
...to a world of suffering,
boundless and eternal.
Tried to stay ahead today to avoid being swept away
流されまいと先回りした今日を
nagasaremai to sakimawarishita kyou wo
But instead got absorbed by yesterday
昨日が吸い込んだ
kinou ga suikonda
With a sigh, I put my feelings aside for now,
ため息　心を後回しにして今日も
tameiki kokoro wo atomawashi ni shite kyou mo
and today, as usual, you jump in with a smile
笑う君は飛び込んだ
warau kimi wa tobikonda
So I pushed back the deadline I'd decided was final
最後ねって決めてたデッドラインを少し延ばした
saigone tte kimeteta deddorain wo sukoshi nobashita
If the view changes after one more step...
あと一歩で景色が変わるのなら
ato iipo de keshiki ga kawaru nonara
Maybe something would change...
何かが変わるのなら
nanika ga kawaru no nara
Shine brightly with all you've got, even if others may laugh at you,
一番に光れ　笑われても
ichiban ni hikare warawarete mo
because I will be holding your hand
手を繋いでいるから
te wo tsunaideirukara
It can't be just someone, it must be you
誰かじゃなくて　あなたじゃなくちゃ
dareka janakute anata janakucha
Only you can save those tears
その涙は救えない
sono namida wa sukuenai
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
I'll be singing for you, waiting for you
あなたに歌ってる　待ってる
anata ni utatteru matteru
I'll be here, singing and waiting for you
この場所で歌ってる　待ってる
kono basho de utatteru matteru