Even now, there is someone choking back tears
誰かが変な涙を 飲み込んで 呑み込んでいる
dareka ga hen na namida wo nomikonde nomikondeiru
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力がこの裏 悪意振り解いて
chikara ga kono ura akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
Look out for these tiny hands
小さなこの手は今
chiisana kono te wa ima
Everything I've fallen in love with
愛してしまった全部全部
aishiteshimatta zenbu zenbu
Including all the curses that have befallen me
降りかかった呪いも全部
furikakatta noroi mo zenbu
All of my feelings for my loved ones
もう愛してしまった想いを全部
mou aishiteshimatta omoi wo zenbu
Give me enough light to protect them
守れるほどの光を
mamoreru hodo no hikari wo
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力が伴う悪意振り解いて
chikara ga tomonau akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
The shadows are closing in, asking, "What are you?"
影は迫る"お前はなんだ"と
kage wa semaru "omae wa nanda" to
Ranking of Kings
Episode 22
A Promise to the Demon
[BOSSE]
Daida.
- Daida.
- [DAIDA gasps]
I know that voice.
[BOSSE] There's something...
I'd like to show you.
[BOSSE] Memories of
my life with Miranjo.
[MIRANJO sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
[groans]
[gasps]
Miranjo!
Raugh...!
[huffing]
[BOSSE sobbing]
[MIRANJO wails]
[BOTH wailing]
[BOSSE]
After that, the two of us saw
much of the world together.
[chuckles]
It tastes good.
It truly is a blessing
to share this life with you.
[BOSSE] Before, my dream was
to become the strongest man
in the world, and the path
was treacherous and bloody.
But I enjoy this tranquility.
[MIRANJO]
He dreamed of greater strength,
and I want him to
accomplish his dream.
But how do I help him?
Would he be
better off if I left?
[sobbing]
No, I can't!
[BOSSE gasps]
Is there something wrong?
[sobbing]
Bosse... You don't need
to worry about me anymore.
Ah.
[MIRANJO]
I want to help you now.
So you can follow your dream.
[BOSSE huffing]
[MIRANJO]
I see you won again.
[BOSSE]
Mm.
I find no satisfaction in battle
unless my life is at stake.
None of the opponents you've
chosen for me have posed
any semblance of a threat.
I want a challenge.
There are stronger foes.
Indeed, there are.
[BOSSE] Tell me who can
push me to my limits.
In this country...
...there's one
called Chabi-shin.
[BOSSE]
Heh.
[MIRANJO]
Ah...
[MIRANJO gasps]
Bosse!
[BOSSE] His power was
on a different level.
[BOSSE]
I don't regret facing him.
[BOSSE] So then, shall we
return to the island?
Don't give up yet, Bosse.
I know of a way we can still
make your dream come true.
[DEMON 3A]
It's been a long time.
Eh, Miranjo?
[gasps]
[MIRANJO whimpers]
[DEMON 3A] It seems like any
time I grant a person's wish,
my body will be twisted
into something more monstrous.
It's okay, 'cause I'm never
gonna ask you for anything.
[MIRANJO whimpers]
[DEMON 3A] I don't appreciate
you making that face at me.
Forgive my rudeness.
I see...
[laughs]
[MIRANJO]
Tell the demon your wish.
My only wish is to become the
strongest man in all the world.
Very well. I shall take
the strength of your child
yet unborn, and grant it to you.
[DAIDA]
The strength... of his child?
[gasps]
Father's power was
stolen from...
[grunts]
[sobs]
Oh, Brother!
[grunts]
[growls]
How dare you, Father?!
[BOSSE grunts]
[BOSSE]
What is... this emptiness?
The fire within me...
Where has it gone?
[BOSSE]
My end has come...
I've betrayed... everyone I've
cared for--you most of all.
I'm sorry.
Now, I'm dying, and leaving you
saddled with these regrets.
[MIRANJO]
No.
We have a chance to start again.
In the form of Prince Daida.
[gasps]
[BOSSE]
Daida?
[laughs]
I hope you'll take
good care of him for me.
He takes after me far more
strongly than his brother.
[BOSSE] His choices will
not always be wise ones.
But I know he'll be
of great help to you
if he has the opportunity.
And he'll treasure you
in his heart, without a doubt.
[gasps]
[DAIDA screams]
[BOSSE]
Daida...
Daida.
[BOSSE] Please...
Look after Miranjo for me.
[DAIDA grunts softly]
Father...?
[DEMON 3A laughs]
[SOULS screaming]
[MIRANJO whimpering]
[SOULS laughing]
[MIRANJO sobbing]
- [BOJJI] Au!
- [HAKURO] Ah?
Ah, au!
- My crossbow. Right!
- Au!
[DESPA]
Brother!
[DEMON 3A chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
[laughs]
Huh?
[CAPTAIN 5A gasps]
Captain!
[CAPTAIN 5A snarls]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
It's mine!
If you want your head back...
...then you'll grant me
this wish in return!
Wait, he's making a wish?
I will hear your wish.
Tira ehl lah sin eht.
Heh. I wish for my brother
Ouken to be freed from the―
[gasps]
Ee-ah-oh! Ee-ah-oh!
[DESPA]
Hmm? "Save Miranjo"?
- [DAIDA] Demon!
- [BOTH gasp]
Here is my wish!
[MIRANJO]
Ah...
[gasps]
Revive her.
Let Miranjo live again!
[DAIDA growls]
Everything is okay.
Now then, shall we go?
Why, King Bosse?
After I...
Not to be rude, but it's Daida.
[gasps]
[BOJJI]
Au-ah!
It was good to see you, Miranjo.
[MIRANJO sobs]
I'm sorry, old friend...
Someday, I swear...
I'll make you yourself again.
That boy stole our wish
from under our noses!
- Heh, heh!
- [gasping]
[laughing]
- [DAIDA growls]
- [laughing continues]
It worked!
[gasping]
[laughs]
[DESPA grunts]
Oh!
[CAPTAIN 5A clears throat]
[MIRANJO grunts]
[DAIDA gasps]
[MIRANJO]
King Daida...?
[gasps]
That's right.
You've been
brought back to life!
[MIRANJO gasps]
Thank you. You lent
me your strength,
and allowed me to
persevere in the darkness.
For so long, I've wished
to meet your true self.
[MIRANJO]
But... I did... all of this...
That's exactly it!
You helped me grow.
You've made me stronger!
[MIRANJO gasps]
Miranjo...
May I have your hand
in marriage?
[MIRANJO whimpers]
You... You can't really mean...
[DAIDA]
I do.
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
Everyone, listen to me!
You shall henceforth
refrain from hostilities
against my betrothed!
[CAPTAIN 5A growls]
[snarls]
What is this madness?!
Stay your hand!
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Eh?!
We'll do everything we can
to make amends.
But please...
I beg you to forgive her.
[CAPTAIN 5A snarls]
We came to save Prince Ouken,
and that wish
was rightfully ours.
We can't just let this go!
This woman will repay
what you've stolen from us!
[DAIDA grunts]
[OUKEN] Brother, the time for
you to save me is yet to come.
There are others far more
in need of saving than me.
Oh, Ouken...
Is this what you meant before?
[DESPA laughs]
Fine. We accept.
[gasps]
[DESPA]
But in her place...
...we'll take our compensation
in the form of silver and gold!
Ah.
[CAPTAIN 5A]
Prince Despa!
[DESPA]
Ouken is very much alive.
There are more
opportunities to come.
You are not yet absolved,
young lady.
I've seen memories
of the life you lived,
and the pain you endured.
[MIRANJO whimpers]
[DESPA] So. Having been
so badly wronged,
and having wronged so many,
go and share your story with
the generations to come.
Perhaps you can save them
from such tragedy.
Let that be your purpose.
Atone for your sins by
sparing others from suffering.
[gasps]
[DESPA] Hmm. Indeed,
build upon the happiness
of those around you,
and you'll be sure to find
happiness for yourself.
[MIRANJO whimpers]
[MIRANJO sobbing]
[DESPA]
Are you satisfied?
[CAPTAIN 5A grunts]
[sighs]
[BOJJI]
Au!
[KAGE] That was such
a nice thing to say!
- [gasping]
- [DESPA] Easy, now. [laughs]
[gasping]
[DAIDA]
Thank you very much.
For what you did today, and for
all you've done for my brother.
[BOJJI]
Uh.
I only offered Bojji
a broader perspective toward
his own capabilities.
In fact, he'd been quietly
honing his skills for years
before he and I ever had
the chance to meet.
His efforts were
rarely noticed,
and he was often dismissed,
but he believed in himself.
I'm glad he did, and that
he found a fine teacher.
[BOJJI]
Mm.
Wah!
[KAGE giggles]
[CAPTAIN 5A] What will
we report to King Desha?
[gasps]
Hmm...
[CAPTAIN 5A] The chance
to save Prince Ouken
has slipped from our grasp.
[DESPA sighs] I suppose
we'll tell him the truth,
and see how he responds.
[DESHA]
What did you say?
[growls]
[JUDGE 4A gasps]
[DESHA groans]
Nothing for it.
We'll demand an embarrassment of
silver and gold as compensation!
[DESPA gasps]
But, Brother...
[DESHA]
But what?
Is there anything
else we can do?
[DESPA]
No. I understand.
He doesn't plan on punishing us.
[CAPTAIN 5A gasps]
[DESPA]
But why...?
Why would he let this go?
I accept your offer of the
first place in the Ranking.
Take me to the treasure
vault at once.
[gasping]
[DORSHE]
Queen Hiling.
It's over.
Everything's resolved.
What do you mean?
Daida, right?
Yes.
I heard you, Mother.
Your voice was always with me!
[gasps]
[DAIDA]
You were there, weren't you?
Calling to me over and over!
[HILING whimpers]
- Nonsense!
- Uh...
Anyway, what exactly
is going on here?
[DAIDA]
Hmm.
Brother returned.
And helped bring me back.
[gasps]
[HILING]
Hmph.
[DORSHE]
Uh. Queen Hiling?
Hah. I would expect
nothing less.
I knew I would see him again.
There's no challenge
Bojji won't overcome.
Now, here.
You fought bravely,
as befits your station.
Great work!
You're both...
[whimpering]
...my boys!
- My sweet boys!
- Please, Mother!
I'm too old for this kind
of smothering affection!
Don't you talk back to me!
And no objections
from you, either!
[HILING whimpers]
You did so well!
The rest of you
appear to be fine.
Good. That's a relief.
[KAGE chuckles]
- [HILING] Wait.
- [KAGE] Hmm? Ugh―
[HILING]
Who is she, again?
[MIRANJO] I'm sorry...
I'm the cause of all this―
[DAIDA]
Well, Mother.
She's the one responsible for
trapping me in the darkness.
[gasps]
What's more, she set this entire
chain of events into motion.
[gasps]
She's behind everything?!
Are you telling me
this strange woman is...
...Miranjo?
[DORSHE]
Your Majesty!
I will have her head!
Wait, Mother.
I have decided to
take her as my wife.
Eh?
What...?!
There's no telling
what's to come.
You'll be in charge here.
Sire.
Be assured, King Desha.
No harm will befall you,
regardless of what
you decide hereafter.
[JUDGE 4A] Though you
might undergo a change,
as people do when granted
immense wealth and power,
or when faced with
something beyond what
they had dared to imagine.
Heh.
[JUDGE 4A] You have obligations
to those you rule.
Yet you accepted your place atop
the Ranking in a selfish bid
to save your brother, Ouken.
You, yourself,
are ruled by your desire.
By desire, eh?
[JUDGE 4A]
Even if you benefit,
the Ranking of Kings exists for
the happiness of the people.
That's what I believe
to be its true purpose.
[DESHA growls]
Tried to stay ahead today to avoid being swept away
流されまいと先回りした今日を
nagasaremai to sakimawarishita kyou wo
But instead got absorbed by yesterday
昨日が吸い込んだ
kinou ga suikonda
With a sigh, I put my feelings aside for now,
ため息　心を後回しにして今日も
tameiki kokoro wo atomawashi ni shite kyou mo
and today, as usual, you jump in with a smile
笑う君は飛び込んだ
warau kimi wa tobikonda
So I pushed back the deadline I'd decided was final
最後ねって決めてたデッドラインを少し延ばした
saigone tte kimeteta deddorain wo sukoshi nobashita
If the view changes after one more step...
あと一歩で景色が変わるのなら
ato iipo de keshiki ga kawaru nonara
Maybe something would change...
何かが変わるのなら
nanika ga kawaru no nara
Shine brightly with all you've got, even if others may laugh at you,
一番に光れ　笑われても
ichiban ni hikare warawarete mo
because I will be holding your hand
手を繋いでいるから
te wo tsunaideirukara
It can't be just someone, it must be you
誰かじゃなくて　あなたじゃなくちゃ
dareka janakute anata janakucha
Only you can save those tears
その涙は救えない
sono namida wa sukuenai
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
I'll be singing for you, waiting for you
あなたに歌ってる　待ってる
anata ni utatteru matteru
I'll be here, singing and waiting for you
この場所で歌ってる　待ってる
kono basho de utatteru matteru