Even now, there is someone choking back tears
誰かが変な涙を 飲み込んで 呑み込んでいる
dareka ga hen na namida wo nomikonde nomikondeiru
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力がこの裏 悪意振り解いて
chikara ga kono ura akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
Look out for these tiny hands
小さなこの手は今
chiisana kono te wa ima
Everything I've fallen in love with
愛してしまった全部全部
aishiteshimatta zenbu zenbu
Including all the curses that have befallen me
降りかかった呪いも全部
furikakatta noroi mo zenbu
All of my feelings for my loved ones
もう愛してしまった想いを全部
mou aishiteshimatta omoi wo zenbu
Give me enough light to protect them
守れるほどの光を
mamoreru hodo no hikari wo
Cast aside the power that comes with malice
力が伴う悪意振り解いて
chikara ga tomonau akui furi hodoite
Despite being deaf
耳は聞こえちゃいない
mimi wa kikoechainai
But the hero doesn't need power right now
だが勇者は今 力は要らない
daga yuusha wa ima chikara wa iranai
Just leave it to yourself
身に任せて
mi ni makasete
The shadows are closing in, asking, "What are you?"
影は迫る"お前はなんだ"と
kage wa semaru "omae wa nanda" to
Ranking of Kings
Episode 23
The King and the Sun
[DAIDA]
Mother.
I've decided to take
Miranjo as my wife.
- [HILING] H-Huh?!
- [BOJJI, KAGE gasp]
[DAIDA]
She's committed grievous sins,
but she's suffered grave
injustices herself.
I'll accept her pain,
and the pain she's caused.
I'll forgive it all!
[MIRANJO gasps]
[sobs]
[DOMAS] If King Daida forgives
her, then that's that.
- [HILING] Huh?!
- [APEAS] Hmm!
[HILING gasps]
[BOJJI]
Hmm!
[DAIDA]
No more tears.
I promise I'll
make you happy again.
[DAIDA] I swear, I'll give
you every reason to smile.
[gasps]
[DORSHE gasps]
[HILING chuckles]
[sobs]
[gasps]
[sobbing]
What's wrong?
[MIRANJO sobbing]
I...
I'll try to bring happiness...
to everyone around me...
Good. And I'll change, too.
- [gasping]
- Please forgive me.
I allowed my pride to
get the better of me,
and you all were left to deal
with the consequences.
I wish to make amends.
[BEBIN]
King Daida...
[DOMAS] I never expected
him to show such humility.
[gasps]
[BOJJI whimpers]
What's wrong, Bojji?
[APEAS]
In that case...
[APEAS] ...I ask that
you relinquish the crown
to Prince Bojji.
- [gasps]
- [gasping]
[gasps]
[KAGE]
Ooh...!
Precisely my intention.
[gasping]
[BOJJI]
Ah―
Dear brother, forgive me.
You have my gratitude,
for showing me what it means
to be worthy of the throne.
[KAGE]
Woo-hoo!
[KAGE giggling]
[BOJJI grunts]
[DORSHE]
"I did no such thing."
[DOMAS]
"I'm not that good of a person."
Au... Uh...
[HILING]
It's my fault.
His confidence is gone,
because I stole it from him.
Uh.
[KAGE]
Attention!
Waaah...!
[gasping]
[BOJJI whimpering]
I know you would be
a great king, Bojji!
'Cause I've watched you play
the part with my own eyes!
[gasps]
[KAGE chuckles]
[HILING gasps]
[BOJJI]
Hmm!
- [DAIDA, BOJJI gasp]
- [KAGE] Hmm?
[DOMAS]
Prince Bojji!
We all promise to serve you
with everything we have!
Oh. Guess what, guys?
Bojji's been able to
understand you all along
by reading your lips!
[gasping]
[DOMAS] He's known everything
the whole time, and yet...
[DOMAS] How can he still
believe he's unworthy?
[BEBIN]
He may not realize, but...
[APEAS]
He's more than fit!
Prince Bojji!
Prince Bojji has grown up,
and what an exceptional
young man he's become.
[HILING]
Mm.
[DAIDA whimpers]
My king!
[gasps]
- [KAGE chuckles]
- Ah!
Mm!
Long live King Bojji!
[ALL yell]
[KAGE]
Woo-hoo! You did it, Bojji!
Hmm? Hmm...?
[SORII] And he'll only have
more to do from now on.
[DOMAS] Premier Sorii and
Justice Minister Sandeo!
[BEBIN] Hmph! Where were
you two during all this?
Anyway! We're here now.
So let us celebrate
the crowning of our new king!
- [BOJJI] Huh?
- I agree!
Shall we toss him in the air?
[laughs]
[GROUP]
Yeah!
[grunts]
[APEAS grunts]
[HOKURO]
Ah-ha!
[SANDEO groans]
You can take a break
from dodging, Bojji.
Please, King Bojji?
We'll need your trust
to best aid you in your reign.
[GROUP]
Hmm.
[BOJJI gasps]
- [ALL] Hail...
- [BOJJI gasps]
...to the king!
[BOJJI whimpers]
[GROUP]
Hip, hip hooray!
Hip hip hooray!
- Hip hip hooray!
- [KAGE] Huh...? Huh...
[GROUP]
Hip hip hooray!
So, shall we escort him
to the throne?
[GROUP]
Hmm?
[chuckling]
Yeah!
- [GROUP] Hip, hip hooray!
- [KAGE] Be seein' ya, Bojji.
Hip hip hooray!
[KAGE]
I'm just a common crook...
I've got no business
hangin' around with a king.
[KAGE] He doesn't
need me anymore, right?
[KAGE] Besides, this fancy
castle isn't my style.
[KAGE]
It's a great big world, Bojji,
and you've got
unlimited potential!
[KAGE]
Go for it, bud!
Y'know, when I think about it,
I've got potential myself, huh?
[KAGE]
It's fine.
There's someone out there
who could use my help.
For sure. There's gotta be.
[KAGE]
Even if it's not Bojji.
Who am I kidding?
I know... I'm really the one
who needs him, but I just...
[sobs]
Toughen up, Kage!
You can do this.
You've always survived
in the shadows!
[MAN 23A]
Congratulations, King Bojji.
Au!
[gasps]
[MAN 23B]
King Bojji.
Uh?
Ah-eh!
Ah-eh?!
Is everything all right?
Ah-eh. Eh-oh!
It's Master Kage! He's missing?!
[BOTH]
Mm-mm...
Hold on, Hokuro...
It could be that he left King
Bojji's side of his own accord.
[gasps]
Ah! Careful what you're saying!
Gah! Lipreading!
What on earth
is wrong with you?!
Sorry! I forgot!
- [BOJJI grunts]
- Ah!
[HOKURO, DOMAS]
King Bojji!
Unfortunately, assuming
he disappeared by choice,
he wouldn't have left a trace,
and he'll be near
impossible to find.
[DOMAS] It's not uncommon
for people's paths
through life to diverge.
Rather, it's something of
a miracle when they don't.
Fate rarely lets us walk
the same path to the end.
[KAGE sighs]
[KAGE]
You're gonna be a great king.
Yes, King Bojji?
[KNIGHTS murmuring]
[KINGBO]
I'm quite all right.
Thank you.
[DAIDA] Thanks again
for all you've done.
Well, then. Please give Bojji―
Pardon. King Bojji my regards.
Right.
- [boom]
- [gasping]
[yelling]
[UNDERWORLD KNIGHTS grunting]
[UNDERWORLD KNIGHT 23C]
Kingbo?! Why, you―
[groans]
[UNDERWORLD KNIGHT 23C groans]
No, Prince Ouken is―
[KINGBO]
Heh!
[KINGBO snarls]
[KINGBO grunts]
[KNIGHTS gasping]
[KINGBO laughs]
Our differences are settled now!
[DESPA panting]
Ouken!
[TOWNSWOMAN 23A]
Look, it's the king!
[TOWNSMAN 23A]
King Bojji!
[TOWNSWOMAN 23B]
Long live King Bojji!
[TOWNSMAN 23B]
King Bojji!
- [TOWNSMAN 23C] King Bojji!
- [TOWNSWOMAN 23C giggles]
[inaudible]
[BOJJI]
Hmm!
[SORII]
Very well.
Then we shall proceed
accordingly at once.
Does the king...
look troubled to you?
Yes. I think...
it's Master Kage.
[HILING grunts]
Leave us, please.
I'll speak with him.
[gasps]
Clearly, there's something
weighing on your mind.
Your retainers see it
in your expression,
and they can't help but worry.
That simply won't do!
Your duty is not to your own
feelings, but to your kingdom.
A leader of men must bear
many such burdens.
You know this, yes?
[BOJJI whimpers]
Ah...
[grunts]
[HILING] It just occurred
to me how long it's been
since I last saw your friend.
Ah...
[whimpers]
Ah.
[BOJJI sobs]
[HILING] You dreamed of
becoming king, did you not?
As king, it's your
responsibility to see to
the happiness of your people.
This is what defines
a great ruler.
[KAGE] Whew! I'd say that
turned out pretty good!
[chuckles]
All right. Now I've
got a place to live.
Time to go find
some honest work,
and show the new
Kage to the world!
[chuckles]
[TOWNSFOLK murmuring]
[KAGE]
I'm going straight.
No more stealing.
Ha! They oughta know better
than to underestimate Kage.
Hey! Got a job for me?
[KAGE] Pardon me, but your
sign mentions you're in need
of a shopkeeper.
Hey! Got any work to do?
'Cause I'll do it!
Uh?
[screams]
[panting]
Man, that's rough.
Who knew finding work
could be this hard?
But regardless,
I gotta keep at it!
He was from the shadow clan.
Creepy little thing!
[MAN 23C] They only bring
darkness if you let them linger.
[KAGE]
Guess today didn't go my way,
but there's always tomorrow.
Huh?
My house is wrecked!
Huh? But... I won't
get discouraged.
I can't get discouraged,
no matter what!
[KAGE]
Hmm? Hey!
Huh?
[growls]
The heck?!
[sniffles]
[KAGE snoring]
[gasps, grunts]
[laughing]
Huh? Bojji!
C'mon, cut it out!
Ha, ha! Heh...
[KAGE]
Stop remembering...
Quit looking back...
It'll just make you lonelier...
[sobs]
- [leaves rustle]
- [KAGE gasps]
[KAGE gasps]
I'll always be by your side
♪
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Au!
even in the shadows
[KAGE]
Bojji!
[BOJJI]
Ah-eh!
[KAGE]
Y-Your old traveling clothes?
Hey, what's going on?
We both went through a lot and cried about the same amount
[BOJJI]
Hmm!
[HILING] As king, it's
your responsibility to see
to the happiness of your people.
This is what defines
a great ruler.
Nonetheless, king or not,
if you find something
which truly matters to you,
you ought to pursue that
something with all your heart.
Find the place where
you can shine the brightest,
and make it your own.
Your friend, Kage, was it?
He was like a little sun
whose light shone on you,
and I think he acted as
a bit of a good luck charm.
[BOJJI]
Au-wa-wa?
Right. It's a very
special thing.
A good luck charm will
save you from misfortune,
- so long as you keep it close.
- [gasps]
[HILING] If you protect it,
and always hold it precious
in your heart, soon, you'll find
that it protects you in turn.
[HILING]
You've grown strong and wise,
and spread your light into
the world with the help of
your good luck charm.
That's something I first
learned from my own teacher,
many years ago.
Head forth, and seek
the life you wish to lead.
[HILING]
Bebin!
Journey on... my boy.
My Bojji...
But... wait...
What about the
whole "king" thing?
Ah... Ah, au!
You re-relinquished
the throne to Daida?!
Wha― You dumb or somethin'?!
- [growls]
- What's the deal?
Ah! Au, au!
[KAGE] You're gonna make
like your old man,
and start a brand new
kingdom yourself?
- [BOJJI] Hmm! Hmm!
- Whoa, easy!
[KAGE]
W-Well, sure.
I don't doubt you
could pull it off, but...
[BOJJI]
Hmm!
[HILING]
That child is your sun.
[KAGE]
What? Aw, heck.
So you've still got even
more to learn, is that right?
Meaning we gotta run off on
a whole 'nother journey now.
Hey. You brought
some coin, didn't ya?
Whoo! A king's ransom!
- [BOJJI panting]
- Huh?
Wait! Lemme catch up, Bojji!
Ah, oh!
[KAGE]
Thank you...
...so much!
[KAGE]
Woo-hoo!
[BOJJI]
Ah-eh!
Tried to stay ahead today to avoid being swept away
流されまいと先回りした今日を
nagasaremai to sakimawarishita kyou wo
But instead got absorbed by yesterday
昨日が吸い込んだ
kinou ga suikonda
With a sigh, I put my feelings aside for now,
ため息　心を後回しにして今日も
tameiki kokoro wo atomawashi ni shite kyou mo
and today, as usual, you jump in with a smile
笑う君は飛び込んだ
warau kimi wa tobikonda
So I pushed back the deadline I'd decided was final
最後ねって決めてたデッドラインを少し延ばした
saigone tte kimeteta deddorain wo sukoshi nobashita
If the view changes after one more step...
あと一歩で景色が変わるのなら
ato iipo de keshiki ga kawaru nonara
Maybe something would change...
何かが変わるのなら
nanika ga kawaru no nara
Shine brightly with all you've got, even if others may laugh at you,
一番に光れ　笑われても
ichiban ni hikare warawarete mo
because I will be holding your hand
手を繋いでいるから
te wo tsunaideirukara
It can't be just someone, it must be you
誰かじゃなくて　あなたじゃなくちゃ
dareka janakute anata janakucha
Only you can save those tears
その涙は救えない
sono namida wa sukuenai
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
Shine on toward a yet-unseen tomorrow
まだ見ぬ明日へと光れ
mada minu asu e to hikare
I'll be singing for you, waiting for you
あなたに歌ってる　待ってる
anata ni utatteru matteru
I'll be here, singing and waiting for you
この場所で歌ってる　待ってる
kono basho de utatteru matteru