[CHIO] ♪ There once was
a dog named Chop ♪
♪ who had some
real rank breath. ♪
♪ It smelled like
cheese and death. ♪
♪ He's the cutest mutt
when his mouth is shut, ♪
--[CHIHARU] Hey.
--♪ but look out when he-- ♪
[CHIO]
No way.
She's at my house.
She has my address.
She's stalking me.
She's planning a raid
with her rich-kid homies.
Oh, hey there. Are you
lost or something?
[gasps] I really don't have time
for random acts
of violence right now.
I've gotta get to school!
That move only works when you
grab someone by their collar!
[CHIHARU]
Shut up!
'Kay!
I need to know if
you're smart or not.
Compared to what?
If you're going by grades,
I'd say I'm average.
[CHIO] And by that,
I mean below average.
I see. I'm having trouble
with my homework.
Huh?
That sucks.
[CHIHARU] My brother
can't study for squat,
and besides him, you're the only
older person I know to ask.
[CHIHARU]
Stare...
Ooh? Oh, um, I guess
I could try to help you?
Good.
[CHIO]
Seriously?!
Did she just "good" at me?
What an entitled little shit!
Gimme your homework, kid.
I'll teach you not to
mess with the advanced
high-school cranium!
[dog barks]
[CHIO]
A diagram. Yeah. Sure.
Uh--huh? Huh?! What?!
--[CHIHARU] Stare...
--Okay, this is way harder
--than I expected.
I forgot she goes to
Eihei Girls Academy.
Super advanced prep school
for high-dollar girlies.
I'm trapped. I need a
way out. What do I do?
Wait, that's not it.
I gave you the easy one.
While we're paused,
can you tell me how
you found my address?
I borrowed Mayu's computer and
I noticed he had a map open
with your house
clearly marked on it.
Okay. Makes sense!
[CHIO]
The hell?
Okay. Here, found it.
[CHIO]
Awesome.
It looks like this is from
your social studies class?
[NARRATOR]
Using your current abilities,
explain how you would earn
500 yen within 24 hours.
[CHIO]
Whoa, this is hardcore!
Damn, Eihei! You're out to make
the youngest lady-entrepreneurs
in the history of ever!
Gotta admit,
that's kinda awesome.
Okay, so how would
I answer as Chiharu?
What could I-slash-she
do to make money?
--Go.
--[FEMALE VOICE 8A moans]
[MAN]
Hot school girl.
Thanks. That's 20K.
[CHIO]
I just mentally pimped her out.
I'm the worst!
Just curious, what did you
come up with for this answer?
[CHIHARU]
That's why I need help.
Apparently, my ideas
just weren't good enough.
Mug someone.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
Mugging is the action
in which one forces another
to give them their money.
Sorry. No indisputably
criminal acts.
However, many
successful businesses
have questionable origins,
so you may keep that in mind.
[STUDENTS]
'Kay!
So, yeah.
[CHIO]
Sounds a little shady.
[ANDOU] Five hundred yen in one
night without mugging someone?
I guess you could
look for a parked bike
to rip up and sell the parts.
Just make sure
it's not well lit.
I would've gone with that,
but I've never
taken apart anything
and I would need more than
a single day to figure it out.
How did you answer this
when you were in my grade?
Tell me now!
[laughs]
[CHIO]
Now's my chance.
I'll teach this stuck-up a-hole
how to be a woman with dignity!
I'll be the wind
beneath her wings.
Hello?
[CHIO]
Come with me.
There's only one sure way
to master this task.
[CHIHARU]
What's all that?
[CHIO chuckles]
[CHIO]
Every can my dad's ever drained.
Someone I know
once taught me this.
You mean for cash?
All these empty cans
can be a gold mine,
but you've gotta
be smart about it.
He said there's a factory
around here that buys them.
Okay.
I'm about to start
your college fund
with the "Get Rich Quick
by Selling Recyclables" plan!
Not only are you
saving the planet,
but you're also totally slaying
your assignment, right?
I guess so.
You're smarter than you look.
Yeah, duh! I just have way
more experience than you do!
[CHIO] Real talk, it's like,
three or four years.
[yells]
Do we have to flatten
every single one?
Uh, work ethic! Yes!
You should only sell things
in their best condition.
That's common sense!
They're gonna flatten them
during the recycling
process anyway,
so we're doing a solid
by saving them time.
Plus, when they're flat,
they take up less space
so they're easier
for us to carry.
Win-win!
Yeah, I think I get it.
So cool! It's like
how they remove
all the water from
orange juice to make it
lighter for transport!
Stop screaming.
I'm trying to further
my education.
Do we separate the hard
cans from the soft ones?
[CHIO]
And she's hooked.
Just keep the hard ones.
You know what they always say.
The harder the better, right?
That's why diamonds
are so damn expensive.
You could've just said yes.
[CHIO]
Okay, you ready?
[CHIHARU]
I dunno.
Makin' that paper!
[CHIHARU]
Sure.
[BOY 12A panting]
[BOY 12A]
Yeah!
[CHIO pants, grunts]
[BOYS]
Uh...
What the...
It's what you get in exchange
for wasting my time
with three useless kilos
of frikkin' steel cans!
Did you have to
smash them all first?
It screws with our machines
when we press them through!
It's different here.
What?
[HEBINO] Next time,
just bring aluminum cans!
They're worth ten times more!
Is no one teaching
kids how to recycle?
The aluminum cans
were the softer ones
you said not to pick up.
You said only the hard ones.
[CHIO]
No, I didn't.
Yes-huh, because you said
that thing about diamonds
being the hardest.
[CHIO]
I never said that.
And then you said they'd be
worth more if we flattened them.
No, I said they'd
be easier to carry!
Okay, stop screaming, Four Eyes.
This was your mistake
and you need to take
responsibility for it.
--Apologize.
--Wasn't me.
I'm gonna need you to speak up.
Hey. Don't put all this on me.
You could've just
looked it up yourself.
And it's a written
assignment, right?
So just write that you sold
all the aluminum ones
and don't mention
anything about steel!
I mean, duh. It's not
like I... [sobs]
[CHIHARU]
No way. Are those tears?
Are you actually
crying about this?
Yes, I am! 'Cause we
only made 50 yen!
Wait, seriously?
Hey, cut it out.
We can use the money to buy
you some chocolate, okay?
[CHIHARU]
Damn. One thing I did learn
is that she was never
Mayu's girlfriend.
She's too much of a
wiener to hang with him.
I'd say that was
worth today's trouble.
All right, suck it up.
We're in public.
[CHIO] 'Kay. What's that
line for? Is there cake?
[MANANA gasps]
[CHIO]
Whoa! Manana!
[MANANA]
Hey. Andou's sister?!
[CHIO]
What are you doing here?
[MANANA] The shop up ahead
is having a psychotic sale.
Come take a selfie with me!
[CHIO] What?! Are you
dropping out of school now?
Nah, I'm not. Just skippin'.
--We never discussed that!
--Ow!
--I'm not walking by myself!
--That's my arm skin!
Am I just supposed to hang out
and talk to myself
at lunch, then?
Grow up! You can sleep
at your damn desk!
Do you even know that store?
How are you gonna buy anything?
It's bougie as hell and
your allowance is nothing!
You'd end up standing
in that line all day
just to maybe buy a
coaster for 200 yen!
I could get two coasters.
Manana! You're coming with
me or I'm telling on you!
What, like, you're nine
years old? Stop pulling me!
Don't make me lose my spot!
If I have to leave then I'm
selling my place in line
before I go!
[CHIHARU]
Ah!
Someone's gotta
buy me out first!
You're not gonna ruin this
for me this time, Chio!
[SHOPPER 12A]
I'm interested!
I'd love to buy that spot
from you. How much?
I would buy it
for a thousand yen!
[SHOPPER 12A]
I'll pay 1,500 yen!
[SHOPPER 12B]
Fine. What about 2,000 yen?
[SHOPPER 12A]
How about 2,500?!
Why does it feel like
someone just paid bank
to take my place in line?
Oh, that's right,
because they did! Baller!
Being a line agent would
cost nothing to start
and would only require standing.
Even I could do it!
It's perfect.
[MANANA]
Hm?
It's perfect!
Quit smiling at me.
Turns out you're amazing!
Yeah. I know.
[CHIHARU] And she's the one
who knocked my brother out
with one punch before, too.
She's the real badass!
--[CHIO mumbling]
--We gotta bail.
Something is up
with Andou's sister.
More than usual.
She was almost nice,
and I don't trust that bitch
as far as I can throw her.
--Uh, are you mumbling?
--And that means I need Manana--
I was thinking out loud
and you owe me...
...my cut of the line money.
Huh?
You're kidding, right?
If I hadn't been walking
by and approached you,
you'd still be in line
and you never would've
sold your spot.
Come on!
[CHIO]
I'll settle for half.
[CHIHARU] She was involved
for maybe two minutes
and wants that big of a slice?
[MANANA]
No! Get out of my face!
Fine! Then just give me a third!
You have to admit I
earned some of it, too!
Come on, Manana!
Don't be a stingy-mingy!
[CHIHARU] She may be older than
me, but she's not any wiser.
She thinks she's so smart,
can't accept blame
when she messes up,
and she's shady when
it comes to money.
Man! How could I have
been so stupid?
To think this pathetic
four-eyed worm
is anyone my brother
would have ever liked.
[YUKI]
Chio's School Road !
Why's it so hard
just to turn some coin?
'Cause you're not a pimp.
You should do one of
those nerdy streams
where they pay to watch
you play video games.
Won't work.
If it's not a game
that's popular,
it's hard to monetize it.
Also, way too much competition.
Does that mean you've tried it?
Nope.
Yeah, right.
Don't look me up.
I was curious about the word
"streak" in "kill streak,"
so I did a search.
[MANANA] I woulda looked
up the whole word.
What the hell's a "kill streak"?
[CHIO]
It's--whatever.
The point is that I ended up
on the word "streaking."
[MANANA]
So?
[CHIO] So it's this
societal protest thing
where people run around
the city completely naked!
It was a really effective way
to make a point in the '70s.
They took their clothes off
when they wanted to
be taken seriously?
Man, people back then
were total idiots!
Were they? I dunno.
Can you imagine how
great that would feel?
[MANANA, CHIO]
Nope. Not interested.
So you wanna be a
modern-day streaker?
[gasps] No, I was just thinking
about the tingling feeling
that covers my body when I run.
I wanna become one with the wind
and feel it all
over my bare skin!
[CHIO]
One with the wind?
[CHIO] You're that girl
that has to strip
when she gets to her room, huh?
Oops. I didn't know
I admitted that.
[CHIO]
I knew it!
[CHIO] You didn't before.
I just... Yeah.
What? Oh, no!
Should I not have said
anything? Is it bad?
I mean, at least I wear
an apron when I'm eating!
[MANANA, CHIO]
Cool. Aren't aprons supposed to
protect your clothes?
[CHIO] So, either she eats
her meals in her bedroom
or she's wandering around
her entire house in the nude!
I knew something was up.
No one is that perfect!
[CHIO gasps]
Did you tell anyone else
in our class about all this?
No, it's never really
come up before,
but that's not a bad idea!
I'm pretty sure there
are lots of people
who'd be into the naked life.
Sounds like she's
a bad influence.
My parents love
this lifestyle, too.
And so are her parents!
Hey guys! Whatcha playing?
Think I can join you?
Sure! It's a game
called Ghost Blitz!
[CHIO]
Even though Yuki's
the most popular
girl in our class,
she's always down to hang out
with the below-average
girls like us.
And that keeps me from being
harassed by the normies.
Because she plays a big part
in my day-to-day survival,
it's important that I keep her
as a defe--as a friend!
I've gotta stop her
from telling the world
so Toms don't start peeping
outside her window!
I know it might
hurt her feelings
and she'll think
I'm judging her,
but this is called
tough love, damn it!
--Okay. Here's the thing.
--I was about to tell her...
At last someone gets it!
I'm always naked at my place!
She doubled down on her
desperate ass-kissing,
traitor-bitch, lying game!
[MANANA laughs]
[MANANA] And by "always"
I mean every time I
get out of the bathtub and
walk to the towel rack.
Is that true, Manana?
Tell me. Honestly.
[MANANA gasps]
[YUKI] You wouldn't happen to
be making fun of me, right?
That would be... unfortunate.
My parents raised me to love
my body the way it was made.
We weren't created with
clothes on, you know.
It's fine if you
don't understand.
But I've been taught
that it's also fine
to stand up for myself.
So... I can trust you, right?
You walk around the house as
nature intended, like I do?
[stammering]
[MANANA]
Shit piece!
Yeah, I totally agree with you!
I mean, what are we even
doing? 'Cause after all,
these clothes are just
forcing us to live in denial!
I mean, I just wish
I could, uh...
I wish I could at least stop
wearing underwear to school.
[CHIO]
Girl, hope you're prepared
to sit in that mess
you just made.
--[gasps]
--[CHIO] Huh?
Oh, my god! That's my
wish, too! [giggles]
[MANANA]
Wait. Where we going?
--[YUKI] This'll be so fun!
--I peed before I left--
[MANANA] Never realized
how itchy this material was.
It's riding up my crack.
Thanks for waiting!
You're free-ballin', aren't you?
[CHIO] Bitch! You're literally
stripping for likes!
--[BOYS laughing]
--[YUKI] You ready to get going?
--[MANANA] Oh, yeah.
[MANANA gasps]
Eep!
That was funny, wasn't it?
You're fine.
I'm proud of you, friend.
For what?! This is way scarier
than I thought it would be!
You took control today!
Now work it hard!
Huh? Look, a cockroach!
What? Where?
Right there. You see it?
No! Is it on me?
Looking good, girl!
Wait, there was no roach at all?
If you think that's funny,
wait till you see this!
It's called a wind wedgie,
custom designed
for jerks like you!
[YUKI laughing]
It tickles!
[MANANA] At least some
kid's not running by!
[MANANA, YUKI laugh]
It's not bad when
you get used to it.
Right?
Yeah. I think it's important
to have ventilation.
It's making me walk with my
legs closer together, too.
Like the most feminine
baby deer you've ever seen.
I love how free the
wind makes me feel!
I may start running
at any moment!
Eh. Don't do that.
Everyone will see your muff.
And running that much is
super bad for your knees.
Do you really think so?
Sho' nuff!
[CHIO] Are they, like,
bonding over this? Rude.
Don't you dare, unless
you want it done to you!
You let go first.
Like I would trust you after
that cockroach stunt you pulled!
Butt slap!
Uh...
Um, I don't appreciate being
touched by someone like you
so please respect my space.
Something wrong?
[MANANA]
Nah, just gassy.
[CHIO]
What the hell?
So, if one of them bungee
jumped off a tower,
does that mean the
other would, too?
And just because I don't,
that makes me the boring one?
Wait! Cancel that.
I'm adventurous, damn it!
I need a different analogy!
[CHIO]
See? Now this is exactly it.
Like two slaves
giggling to each other
about how cute and fun their
chains on their legs are!
Who does that?
My chains really are the cutest.
I just got mine yesterday.
[CHIO] And then they
start judging the one
who values their independence!
Look at that chainless loser!
[YUKI]
Poor thing.
Ugh! You're slaves in captivity!
This is not "hashtag goals"!
[BOTH laughing]
[CHIO] Wow. I haven't seen
Manana laugh like that
in a long time.
Bitch, I'm fun, too!
[CHIO] Sorry I didn't ditch
my drawers to be like Yuki.
How does airing out your
cooter make you superior?
Undies are like a conscience.
They restrain your wild side
so you don't end up
arrested or pregnant.
If you throw them away, then--
then you're welcoming
new life experiences!
Good morning.
Hi. Can I... use your restroom?
[MANANA, YUKI laughing]
[CHIO]
Manana! Yuki! Check it!
[BOTH gasp]
[MANANA]
Seriously?
[CHIO] You think you're
living on the edge?
Get real.
Check this out!
Holy shit! This is awesome!
[BOTH]
Slay, bitch, slay!
[giggles]
[CHIO] I've never felt
so in touch with myself.
Later, undies.
I'm lettin' freedom ring!
Lovely to see you
three frolicking about.
[ALL gasp]
You all look radiant today.
I can't explain it,
but something's different--
almost delicious.
[MADOKA sniffs]
[CHIO]
Shit just got real.
I didn't think about
running into Kushitori
in our current state of undress.
If she finds out we've all let
the cats loose in the yard,
we'll never get to school!
Thank you! It's a benefit of
being a first-year student!
We're still too young
for our skin and spirits
to have been destroyed
by our poor life choices!
No surprise. You three have
always had a savory glow.
--I know!
--Sure!
[CHIO]
Time to GTFO.
[MADOKA]
I know! Let's play kabaddi!
[CHIO]
Hell no!
Listen, that spark from within
is coming from an abundance
of unused energy!
If you don't get it out,
you'll turn rude
and get wrinkles!
If you won't play kabaddi,
which sport will you play?
--E-sports?
--Or sumo?
Wrong! The answer's kabaddi!
Sounds like fun!
[MANANA, CHIO scream]
All right. This is our line.
As always, ladies first.
--We're gonna take you down!
--Slow your roll!
[CHIO] Whoa! Don't forget
not all lines are secure!
Looks like Yuki's the
raider. Bring it on!
Okay!
[CHIO, MANANA gasp]
[CHIO yells]
Hell yeah!
Nice tackle, Miyamo!
For someone who complains
as much as you do
about kabaddi, you--[gasps]
Hey! You're out of bounds!
[MANANA]
Sorry, Kushitori! We held it in
for as long as we could,
but we gotta find a restroom
before we flood the streets!
Thanks for understanding!
[MADOKA] That means one of them
could've burst in my presence
at any moment.
Explains the electricity
oozing from their pores today!
[CHIO]
Oh, come on!
You have to be
more careful, Yuki!
How was I supposed to know
that was out there for
the whole world to see?
You shouldn't have
told her we'd play!
Yeah, I get that now.
Holy crap.
So, there's a story about
someone being fined 300,000 yen
for showing their junk
on the street recently.
That's so much!
[YUKI]
Hm...
[YUKI gasps]
That's VR scrilla!
[YUKI]
So, wait, that's all it costs?
[CHIO, MANANA]
Huh?
[YUKI] I've been holding onto
my New Year's money for a while.
I bet I have enough to
pull it off at least once.
[BOTH]
But why?!
[ALL]
Chio's School Road !
[MADOKA] I can't stop
thinking about that moment.
It's like I missed something
important, but what?
Which sport will you play?
--E-sports?
--Or sumo?
[echoing] Or sumo?
Sumo, sumo, sumo...
[MADOKA gasps]
[MADOKA]
Women's sumo wrestling?
Why didn't I say yes to that?!
[NARRATOR]
Uh, we've got some extra time,
so how about some previews?
[CHIO]
If this is a hunt,
then I'll be the hunting-est
hunter that ever hunted!
[CHIO] Freeze. Just where
do you think you're going?
I love you!
Why, Mayu? What about me?
That bastard shouldn't
be screaming from pipes
this early in the morning.
One thing's for sure, you know
how to hold your liquor.
I see what you did there.
Which sports?
She escaped again!
Huh. You idiot.
Marina, look down!
[MARINA gasps]
Go ahead and act polite,
but I can see your true colors.
[MARINA gasping]
[MARINA shrieks]
That was your last peon.
The Seven Spears are
now all that remain!
I'll come for you in a week!
[NARRATOR]
Mad Dog: Andou Chiharu.
That's big talk for
someone so small!
[NARRATOR]
Thumbelina: Noujou Fuyumi.
Psychopath: Toono Ichigo.
The Assassin of Moriyama:
Ogawara Hibiki.
Two Hands: Takagi Youko.
Typhoon: Aotsuka Makoto.
Teacher Slayer: Hama Éclair.
Colossus: Kairiki Ayame.
[CHIHARU]
I'll win it all for friendship!
[ALL]
Thanks for watching!
[CHIO] Name's Miyamo Chio.
I'm a first-year student
and a fierce member of
the Soft Tennis Club!
There's nothing I hate
more than standing out.
[MANANA]
Oh, man, you were so close!
[YUKI]
Chio, can you hear me?
[CREWMEMBER 12A]
Miyamo, can you sit up for me?
[CHIO]
Don't you dare push me, old man!
[CHIO screams]
[ANDOU] You better have a good
reason to scream like--
[laughing] What the hell?
[DIRECTOR 12A]
All right, cut.
I'll wait.
[YUKI]
Oh, my gosh!
[BOTH gasp]
Let me know if I'm not...
--[MANANA] Sorry! I swear!
--[CHIO] Dude, stop that! Ew!
--I didn't mean to.
--Cut?
And now he looks like
a pathetic joke.
Is that what you just told me?!
[CHIO] Holy crap. He's totally
going to headbutt me!
--[ANDOU grunts]
--I can't move!
[ANDOU groans]
I'm so sorry!
[DIRECTOR 12A] Cut! Someone
fly in a first aid kit.
[ANDOU]
Oh, man. Please forgive me.
[MANANA] The one you
were telling us about?
Spending all my money
on deadbeats!
[MANANA]
Here she comes!
[ANDOU, CHIO groan]
Whoa! Damn, Chio.
[CHIO] Hey! Rude.
Are you calling me fat?
You didn't exorcise anything!
[MANANA gasps]
Seriously?
[CHIO]
Help me up! My arms are dying!
Seriously! Remember me!
--[MANANA laughing]
--[DIRECTOR 12A] Cut!
Do we need to wipe the railing?
What's the problem?