[CHIO panting, laughing]
[CHIO] It's that time
of the month again!
The day my favorite hardcore
western game mag goes on sale!
I refuse to wait until
after school to read it!
[STORE CLERK]
Good mornin'!
[CHIO]
What?
Shut up.
They just moved it!
It's here somewhere!
It has to be!
This is the only
place that sells it.
Do not do this to me!
How are they sold
out this early?
Wow. When did they start
selling this magazine?
This is a boys love book.
'Kay. I get it.
They want some more
diverse customers,
but why they gotta
sacrifice my vices?
"Love is love."
That includes gamers.
[CHIO] They traded my doom
and gloom for dude-[bleep]-dude!
I am not okay.
[NARRATOR]
She's actually much better off
when you consider the types
of western games Chio enjoys.
The protagonists are usually
old thugs with guns,
and the heroines
are typically junkies.
The best part is when the aliens
start operating on his legs
with a buzz saw and you can see
all the veins spill out!
[NARRATOR]
They're full of violent images.
These genres aren't
popular in Japan.
But, the few fans that exist
suffer regularly
for their passion.
[CHIO] No localized version
for a game this popular?
[NARRATOR]
Japanese versions can cost
almost double the normal price.
They're taking advantage
of my weakness!
Fine, I'll buy it!
[NARRATOR]
Happens every time.
And so we arrive at
moments like these...
This game sold over 10,000,000
copies around the world,
but it's stupid
impossible to find here
and I need to know why!
Am I the only one in Japan
who understands quality?
Get on my level!
Just so you know,
everyone overseas thinks
JRPG characters are gay AF.
Look at their design!
I mean, why?
That kid handles
a weapon that huge?
Is it supposed to be a metaphor?
And that's not a battle uniform!
That's a profile pic
for a hook-up app!
[NARRATOR] And other displays
of unjustified local resentment.
What's wrong with dudes
who brood and don't shave?
Can't we give them
a chance to be a hero?
Then I could stop
buying Japanese packs
and save for college.
We must demand equality.
For both Japanese
and western games.
Ultra-violence, for world peace.
[BENEDITO] Aren't you interested
in my thick, full lips?
Whoa.
[CHIO] Hmm. I have
to say, I'm impressed
with the variety of characters.
Considering the genre,
I figured they'd all be
skinny pretty boys.
[BENEDITO] To think there's
a place in this country
that's even hotter than my home.
[CHIO]
Damn!
This is way more intense
than I expected,
and I don't mean
the gaming part.
How are they allowed to sell
this in a convenience store?
[FUKUYAMA]
I only know of hell.
[CHIO]
Is this from the same game?
This old guy looks more
like a badass assassin,
but here he is.
I would never
imagine him in here.
He must be undercover.
[FUKUYAMA breathlessly]
Heaven. I'm in... heaven.
[CHIO] I've got 750.
It's for a good cause.
My... education.
Boys love doesn't
do anything for me.
I'm just heightening
my awareness
of other types of gaming.
I'm cultured and worldly and
a GD role model for society.
I'm buying it for research.
So much for trying to pay
for it face-down.
Barcodes ruin lives,
and I'm not in the mood
for judge-y cashiers.
At least I don't
know anyone here.
Great idea on this hot day!
CUSTOMER]
Uh, thanks.
Come back again soon!
[screams]
Frickin' Andou! What the
hell is he doing here?
What happened to slingin' news?
Maybe he's working
both jobs now.
This is a gateway
to awkward conversations.
I'll preserve my
life of anonymity
and come back later.
Shut the front door!
When did that happen?
It must've bent when I slid.
Oh, great.
I broke it, now they're
gonna make me buy it.
Fine!
I got money to spend
in this store.
Their rent's not gonna judge me!
[CHIO crying] But I am!
I'm judging me!
This is wrong!
The only games
I like have corpses!
And what's this ad about?
There's no product!
What if there's
security cameras?
I can't just leave it!
I got this!
I know the perfect way to
get it through the register!
Camouflage style!
[CHIO] It's a technique
used by dude-bros
and passed down for generations
when preparing
to choke the chicken.
You take the [bleep] mag,
cover it with some Shonen junk,
leave the barcode out,
and walk toward the light.
Yay! Shonen whatever-
the-[bleep] is out!
But that means
I have to buy both!
Crap! I only have
about two 210 extra!
That's not enough!
[CHIO crying] I'll have to find
another way buy the BL one.
I just finished convincing
Andou that I'm normal.
Somehow, I'd rather him see me
as a criminal than a BL fan!
I'm gonna have to face
this task head-on.
Hey.
Welcome.
Looks like someone
got a new job!
Oh! Miyamo! I'm happy to
see you! It's been too long!
Oh, uh, yeah, I work
here once a week now.
Oh. That's cool.
[CHIO]
So far so good.
Just hurry and scan the code,
and no one gets hurt.
Hold on!
--[CHIO] Why?
--You can't buy this.
[CHIO] But the sign
said please take one.
It's a free pamphlet
for driving schools!
--[CHIO] Yeah?
--You're too young for a car.
That mean you're gettin' a bike?
Uh... Sure.
[CHIO]
Ah! He's completely exposed!
[muttering incoherently]
[CHIO]
Shit! I don't know anything
about fricking driving school!
I owe it all to you!
Riding on your bike the
other day gave me the itch!
You changed my life.
[ANDOU]
Miyamo, listen.
I think I know
what you want and...
[ANDOU] No. I'm the man.
I should be the one to...
So, can you look through this
and tell me which one
I should go to?
Oh, okay!
[ANDOU]
That was close.
[CHIO] While you're providing
your expert advice.
I must find a way to conceal
the Pecs of No Purpose.
[CHIO] Chocolate! Thank you
for your existence!
I'll take two!
Time for you to get dressed!
That should do it!
No! How did I manage
to make it worse?
--[MAGAZINE MODEL] Chocolate-y.
--It just looks like
I have a thing for
dudes in bikinis
and that I'm planning to eat
chocolate off his paper nips!
Crap!
[CHIO] Scratch that.
It was better before.
Wait. Un-scratch that!
I'm actually onto something!
Turn that candy up!
[CHIO] Bam! Sweet and
sensible tank-top!
In your face, pervy
marketing department!
Mission complete!
[CHIO] Uh, seeing as this might
take you a while to figure out,
here you go.
This is my email.
Let me know if you
find a good one.
[ANDOU]
My heart!
Leave it to me.
I won't let you down.
I gotta get to school, so...
Can you ring me up?
Oh... You mean... Of course.
So, magazine and bunch
of chocolate. Let's see.
I already counted all of them!
This one makes 15!
Fifteen chocolates. So...
Here you go! Take my money!
Your change. Don't spend
it all in one place.
Thanks! I don't need a bag!
I'll just carry it.
You might not want to.
Wait! Um, Miyamo!
I'm really good at reading,
snacking and walking
at the same time, bye.
[CHIO] I am dropping pro-bombs
all over this place!
I rocked this stealth challenge!
Once I'm out of here,
I can hide this in my bag.
[ANDOU]
Hang on, Miyamo!
I didn't do it!
I can't read this part.
Do these first two letters
say BL or LOL?
It's BL, okay?
Okay.
I gotta go now.
--Hold on!
--[CHIO] Hey! What the...
Listen, I'm not
an expert on this,
but those are called
BL games, am I right?
It's fine, but you might
not wanna walk around
flashing that magazine.
Huh?
Look, don't take it
the wrong way.
It's natural for you to
wanna look at cute boys.
It's just, that magazine's
got a reputation
for being kind of pervy.
I don't want some jerk
with issues to see you
and take their
problems out on you.
Also, reading while walking
can be dangerous.
It's your life and
I'm meddling in it.
I'm sorry, but I
worry about you.
Here. Let me...
Hang tight.
Your buddy Andou's
got you covered.
No one will bother you now!
You must be pretty
into this stuff
if you couldn't even wait
till after school
to dig in, huh, Miyamo?
I'm hardcore.
[MANANA] So, you're
either really depressed
or six years old.
Chocolate for lunch?
Yep. It's called
"livin' my best life,"
so don't you judge me.
Too late.
[FUKUYAMA]
Chio's School Road!
[KOHAI]
Seriously.
I don't hear from you for days,
and now you show up
to play video games?
It's not about games, man.
This is research.
You belong to me now.
Got it?
You gotta admit,
it's funny though.
Couple of guys playin'
a sexy bromance game.
I don't mean to make it
awkward. I owe you one.
But I don't think
it's awkward... at all.
[CHIHARU]
Glance. Glance. Stare.
[BOY 7A] Hey, is that an Eihei
Girls' Academy uniform?
Yeah, the private school
for super rich chicks?
You don't usually see
them around here much.
Yeah, right. You mean
in your dreams?
No! They really were
there! Last night!
[MANANA]
BS!
[CHIO]
I saw them with my own two eyes!
What was I supposed
to do, tackle them...
[CHIHARU]
You two!
I challenge you to a duel.
[MANANA] One of your
video game hallucinations.
I don't play games
with monkeys in them.
So how did it get on your roof?
"They." I saw two monkeys.
Okay, fine.
Then, what did the
monkey s say to you?
Act it out.
[CHIO chattering]
Give me a banana!
Then they asked if
they could ride my bike
--and clean my hair.
--[MANANA grunts]
What's the matter? Are you
shocked by the hilarity?
Manana?
There! The stronger-looking
one has been defeated.
That means you're
up next, four-eyes!
Whoa. What the hell?
I challenged you
to a duel, remember?
I sure don't. What are
we dueling about?
I don't think I've ever met you.
Shut up and bend your
ass over, right now!
[CHIO] Are you trying
to give me an enema?
[CHIHARU] Don't you wish!
We have unfinished business!
[CHIO] Huh? How could
I have any business
with someone I don't know?
They do some freaky stuff
in those rich schools.
Is she trying to say
my ass is my face
by having an ass-off
instead of a face off?
Lot of effort
for a witty insult.
I like the way you move.
This isn't your
first ass-off, is it?
[CHIO] She actually
called it an ass-off!
[CHIHARU]
Where'd she go?
Oh, no way!
[CHIHARU] She actually
thinks she can do it!
I never thought
I'd meet another one.
A master of the
sacred technique...
...of two hands.
[CHIHARU] This risky move
requires skillful attacks
and an extended reach.
Fingers often get injured.
We all know the legend
of Takagi from Class Three.
She tried the stance,
but didn't have the strength.
Okay. Where'd you learn that?
Heh. I rarely spill my secrets,
but since you asked nicely,
public grade school.
Well, good thing you have skills
to make up for that mug.
The specs don't help.
You still look stupid.
[MANANA] Eat it. You can
pay for all the times
Chio did that to me.
She's down. What do we do now?
[CHIO] First, this, because
I've always wanted to try it,
and then...
Take her away!
You look psychotic!
[CHIHARU]
Pout.
[CHIO]
Okay, demon child,
tell us your name,
so we can curse it.
[CHIHARU]
Hm...
[CHIO, MANANA]
Uh--?!
Why did you attack us like
some kinda rump renovator?
Silence.
[CHIO, MANANA]
This evil brat!
That's fine.
Can you at least answer
one question for me?
Why are you so into butt stuff?
Would you ask two sumo wrestlers
why they wear thongs
and jump on top of each other?
Wait. Seriously?
That's so not the same.
[CHIHARU]
Fine.
I will never forgive
the dumb girls
from Samejima Academy.
They're the worst.
I started with you because
you looked the most tragic,
and you walk funny.
[BOTH laugh]
[MANANA] Was that supposed
to sound threatening?
'Cause I'm about to piss myself!
[CHIO]
She's like, "You're weak!
Here, serve me my ass
on a pitch fork!"
[BOTH]
Bitch!
[CHIO] You know, she kinda
reminds me of an evil doll.
I'm sure she's part demon.
We're gonna need back up.
I bet we could make everyone
she knows hate her!
We can start by
telling her school
that she's a hoodlum.
Then her parents'll get
involved and she'll be toast.
Ooh, and we should post
a fake medical degree
around her school grounds!
[MANANA]
Like she's a proctologist?
What kinda tools
does an ass doc use?
We'll put 'em in her locker.
For real.
You have got to stop
laughing like that.
[CHIO, MANANA screaming]
[CHIO]
Manana!
Whoopsie. Sorry to crush
your day dreams,
but I just so happen to have
freakish flexibility.
I'm still in the game.
[CHIO yells]
Keep your baby hands off Manana!
Four-eyed POS!
You're about to have
a lot more in common
with that pigtailed porker!
[CHIO]
Hold on.
How did we end up
in the middle of the park?
[CHIHARU] You think this thing
is gonna save your ass?
Shut up! Just chill out.
[CHIHARU] What? What happened
to all your plans to probe me
and call my parents?
Right, about that...
[CHIHARU]
Huh?
Keep your voice down! Please!
[CHIO]
Oh, shit.
Where did all these
people come from?
This does not look good.
I'm playing butt games
with a child.
Come on, gimme your ass, kid.
I'm gonna put my fingers in it!
[WOMAN]
Police!
[CHIO] They're gonna
think I'm a criminal.
A pervy criminal who likes
tying little kids up.
Say your prayers, goat face!
[CHIO]
Keep your voice down, damn it!
You leave me no choice.
Got her.
Now I'll build momentum
and fly us out.
What kind of dance
were they practicing?
No clue.
[CHIO] Thank goodness.
We're away from all the ears.
[CHIO] Now to get her to
the woods and kebab her!
You idiot.
[CHIO] Who lets a tree
get that out of hand?
Damn you, property manager!
Thanks for doing the hard part.
I'll go ahead and
finish you off now.
Sounds like a plan,
but could you please tell
me your motive, first?
And why me? Am I just lucky?
[CHIHARU] Fine. You wanna
know? I'll tell you.
This is revenge
for my older brother!
[CHIHARU]
Who the hell are you?
Let go of me!
[CHIO]
What? Kushitori? Thank you!
But how did you
find me out here?
I heard the cries
of a lady in distress,
and I headed towards them.
--[CHIO yelps]
--The cry of a woman!
[MADOKA] I was in the middle
of kabaddi training
when I heard the
most delightful yelp.
[CHIO]
That's right. This is the park
where she's having
training montages.
I never expected to find
such a cute little bunny
rabbit waiting for me.
[gasps]
Put me down right now!
I'm gonna split you
up the middle!
All right! That sounds like fun!
Here. Have at!
[CHIHARU]
I'm so confused.
Something's different
about this peach tree.
I don't... I don't think
I can go through with it.
[CHIHARU gulps]
[CHIHARU]
If I were to poke her,
I have a feeling it might become
more than just a normal ass-off.
[MADOKA]
Have you learned your lesson?
Don't hurt another woman.
You mustn't be so reckless
in your advances,
as womanhood should
be well preserved.
You need to take care of
yourself, too, lovely maiden.
It's called respect.
[MADOKA] And self-respect
is learning to love
who you truly are.
Playing vulgar games like that
is an insult to yourself.
True dat!
[hisses]
Dumbass. Dumbass.
Dumbass!
So how do you know that girl?
I don't. She attacked
me out of nowhere.
[MADOKA laughs]
How awkward is that?
Well, I better get to
school. See ya later.
[CHIO]
Later!
She saved my ass, literally.
--[CHIO] Manana?
--Bring me the girl.
I've got a surprise for her.
Let's see how much fun
she has with her little game
when she's got screwfingers
giving her an appendectomy!
Creepy. I don't even know you.
[CHIHARU]
Chio's School Road !
Kill her.
I hate that little
freak so much.
That's cool. Sit down.
I can't. I'm sore.
Then eat something.
Don't tell me what to do.
So what's gonna happen
if she comes back?
I'll kill her.
I'm heading to the bookstore.
Wanna come with?
That bitch is gonna pay.
I'm in!
[CHIO]
Impressive.
Huh?
What's the matter?
[MANANA] I've seen that old lady
hanging there a lot lately.
She always seems to be
looking down and sad.
Oh, that's right.
My dad mentioned something
about this place.
See that café across
from where she's sitting?
It used to be a garden with
beautiful hydrangeas growing.
Pretty, aren't they?
[WOMAN]
Yes.
[MAN]
I think, maybe,
we should come back and
look at them once a year.
Together, if you want. So...
We should!
[MANANA] And even after
losing her husband...
[MANANA]
...she still comes here,
looking for remnants
of the past.
It's sad that our society now
doesn't know how
to value memories.
We build boxes of concrete,
steel, and glass
right over them.
Before anyone even notices.
[CHIO] Excuse me, ma'am?
We were wondering,
would you like
some company today?
[video game music playing]
[VIDEO GAME]
You're close!
Keep going, keep going,
keep going! Almost!
[OLD WOMAN]
Aw, shit! I broke my streak!
[EMPLOYEE 7A] Hey! How many
times do I have to tell you
not to sit here
and mooch our WiFi?
I don't wanna be like this,
but that service is
for our customers.
Would it kill you to come in
and have a cup of coffee
while you use it at least?
Screw you! Shut the
door and go to hell!
That's fine.
We'll just make sure
we block your device
if you try to come back!
[laughs]
You do what you want.
I'll hack back into it.
[OLD WOMAN laughs]
Stupid, dumbass kids!
See ya tomorrow!
[CHIO] Next time on
Chio's School Road .
"Yuki Doesn't Care,"
"Chio Fisher,"
and "Momo's Story."
Lookin' forward to it!
I love a chocolate tank top!