Oh, great. I've got indigestion.
Probably a symptom
of sleep deprivation.
But I guess it's better
than getting in trouble
for falling asleep
in the bathroom.
And... here we are again.
I stayed up all night
being a badass online.
I was only gonna play
for 30 minutes.
I gotta go to bed.
[computer beeping]
[CHIO] Oh, cool. It's that
foreign kid who was just on.
Throw this thing in the
translation app, and...
Hm.
Really?! You can't hit me from
there, you frickin' cheater!
You asked for this, dumbass!
[CHIO] It's not my fault
I was provoked.
Morning came outta nowhere.
It's okay, Chio.
I know you're trying.
That's what counts.
[grunting]
[CHIO]
Uh, who's that guy,
and what's he doing?
Maybe he just finished a ride
with his motorcycle gang.
[CHIO] It's totally fine.
He wouldn't waste his time
trying to fight someone
peacefully walking by, right?
I mean, I'm a high school kid.
I guess he could
take my homework.
Oh! No, seriously?
What a jerk!
He's trying to force me to
walk closer to the gangster
because he's scared!
Dude looks like he's got
some important job, too.
Yet despite whatever his
title is, he's a total wuss.
But enough about that.
What kind of ape parks
his bike on the sidewalk?
Just a little bit further.
Don't you dare push me, old man!
[NARRATOR] The exhaust
pipe next to the wheel
is called the muffler.
After riding, it
becomes extremely hot,
over 200 degrees Celsius.
If you were to touch it,
this is the sound you'd make.
[screaming]
[CHIO]
Crap, I think he heard me.
[ANDOU] You better have a good
reason to scream like that, kid.
[CHIO]
He's really big!
[ANDOU]
I take it you wanna fight?
[CHIO] No! I don't! I touched
something really hot
and it made me...
I can't speak!
[laughs nervously]
You must think
you're tough shit,
laughin' in my face like that.
[CHIO] No! It's just what
I do when I'm nervous!
[ANDOU] You know, I've got
a little code I follow.
If you say you wanna fight,
then I won't let you down!
[CHIO] I'm off the ground!
He's gonna kill me!
Help me, you coward!
[ANDOU groaning]
I can't! I've got a part-time
job interview I can't miss!
I'm a winner!
Gotta find a way out of
here before he wakes up.
That's what bit me.
Someone else is gonna run
into it and get burned.
I should move it out of the way.
I'll def need both my
muscles to do this.
Or maybe it'll just
glide outta here.
[whimpers]
[CHIO] Chio, what the hell were
you thinking moving a bike?!
I suck! I suck! I suck!
And now anything that
happens is on me
because it's coated in my DNA!
[groaning]
[CHIO] Of course he
decides to wake up now!
I have to do something!
Let's not forget this
is all his fault!
[ANDOU grunts]
So, you're finally awake.
[ANDOU groaning]
Damn bitch.
That's my bike.
What the hell do ya
think you're doin'?
[CHIO] He can totally tell
which school I go to
by my uniform.
And if I were to run,
he'd catch me
in a matter of seconds.
I just felt like resting
my ass on a piece of junk.
What?!
[CHIO] That might not have
been the smartest thing
I could've said.
But there's no turning back now!
Gonna ride this
thing to the end!
Oh, I know exactly
what I'm doing.
I decided not to
kill you earlier
so we could get
to know each other.
How sad would it be
if you never got to feel
the sting of having
your ass handed to you
by something that looks
like a school girl?
[ANDOU]
What the hell is she then?
She looked like a kid
when she was laughin'.
Fine. But tell me who you are.
Huh, you wanna know my name?
[CHIO]
Aw, man, picking names
is always the hardest
part of starting a game.
I guess I'll just
use my usual one.
Bloody Butterfly.
You made that up! No one's
called "Bloody Butterfly"!
Get over yourself!
[CHIO] Of course, you've
never heard of me!
I'm on a level you
didn't know existed!
While you're out there
with your buddies
playing motorcycle gang,
I'm packin' heat
and shootin' it out
with foreigners all night long.
Eight days a week.
That so?
You're talkin' proxy
wars in the night now?
Oh, no! Don't kill me, eh?
You've lost your mind if you...
[CHIO]
You're lucky I'm in a good mood.
I'm gonna let you go as long
as you throw out this tricycle
and leave the gang.
It's a waste of time.
Here you are, day after day,
fightin' gang after gang,
and for what purpose?
Where does it lead you?
Let me tell you what
I know about this life.
My nights are filled
with the screams
of terrorized jerks
who deserve death,
but my days are
filled with regret.
I've forgotten who I was
before I chose this path.
I've seen guys end up
crippled for life.
You want that? You
wanna wear a diaper
'cause you can't stop
pissing yourself?
Crippled?
I'm tryin' to do
you a favor here.
Don't end up like me.
If I could do it over,
I'd shoot for below average.
It might be a boring life,
but at least then,
you'd have peace.
[ANDOU]
This is absurd.
It's absolutely insane,
but she's so convincing,
I believe her.
You could ignore my
advice if you want,
but what good would it do you
when all you have left
of your masculinity
is this busted pink scooter
some girl destroyed
along with your pride?
[groaning]
[ANDOU grunts]
[ANDOU screams]
[ANDOU]
Okay. You win.
I'll start my new life today.
On one condition.
Before you go,
grant me a final wish.
Would you please join
me for one last ride
as a symbol of our pact,
at least as far as your school?
I did not sign up for this.
It turned out to be a
bigger deal than I thought.
Looks like we're here.
'Kay.
Thank you, Bloody Butterfly!
[ALL gasping]
[STUDENTS]
"Bloody Butterfly"?
Wait.
I've never heard that name.
So, uh, are you sure
you're at the right school?
[in foreign accent] Yes, sir,
I am. It is first day
as exchange student!
I see.
[ANDOU]
Chio's School Road !
Hey, Chio, doesn't it seem like
there are a lot more
couples around lately?
[CHIO]
Hm? Oh, yeah. Weird.
Oh, my gosh, everywhere.
When did that happen?
The saddest part is that
they're all first years.
So you know what
that makes them?
Relationship noobs.
[NARRATOR]
"Noobs" is the term gamers use
for "beginner" or "amateur."
First-year students tend to have
a delusional outlook on love
which leads them
to declare themselves
"in a relationship" with,
well, whomever will agree to it.
But the illusion
eventually fades.
Friends stop calling.
Social media likes
hit single digits.
Then most relationship noobs
break up over summer vacation.
I kinda feel bad for them.
They have no idea
what they're doing.
Just hurling themselves
into battle
without any training
or strategy.
I don't know--what are
your thoughts on all this?
Do it in December.
I'm almost afraid to ask.
You only need to
have one relationship
in your entire
high school career.
If you go out with
more than that,
then it just sounds
like you couldn't keep
your junk to yourself,
and no one will ever love you
when you grow up.
You can't do it anywhere
near the end of high school
because you gotta
focus on graduation.
You wanna aim for the
holiday and event season
when it's more fun to
have someone around.
So, December of your first year
to summer of your second year.
And then you're done. After
that, you focus on your studies
and you never hear
from them again!
Best plan ever!
Chio, that diagram!
It looks familiar.
Ootoro !
Which means...
It's the most delicious
time to date someone.
[NARRATOR]
Warning! This dating advice
is brought to you by two girls
with zero dating experience.
I lied! I was just
trying to be tough--
I wanna know what love is, too!
[CHIO]
You're being really loud.
So, what?
No one's paying attention to us!
[BOTH laughing]
[GIRL]
Yeah, that sounds fun.
Excuse us.
Oh, my god! What are you doing?
They were grossing me out,
so I broke them up,
literally, for, like,
three seconds.
[CHIO] She might be
the worst person I know.
Does that kind of
stuff not bother you?
I guess you wouldn't notice
since you're gaming
all the time.
[CHIO]
I mean, she's got a point.
Uh, hey, isn't that...
...Hosokawa?
[MANANA] Duh. She's the
star of the track team.
Now what?
Full-on ninja attack, or...
No.
Nearing the
popularity atmosphere
results in obliteration
on impact.
[laughs] I totally get that!
We're in the same awkward boat!
[MANANA]
Ugh! Look at them!
They're so disgusting
and perfect!
I don't even hate
that they're both
unrealistically hot, ya know?
[MANANA]
"Look how big my hand is.
I've been lifting
a lot of finger weights
so I can play the bass better."
"Mine is small and dainty.
Perfectly manicured."
"Let's palm bone."
"We'd have beautiful
hand babies.
I think it's so cool
that you play bass."
"Actually, I made that part up.
I'm hot, not talented."
[CHIO] Uh, this hand dub
went downhill real fast.
"...not good enough!
Get it out of my life!"
[car horn honking]
What the what?!
I was not prepared for
chivalrous road walking!
Please, make it stop!
If they start sharing sodas
or wearing each
other's accessories,
I'm gonna electrocute myself!
[BOTH]
Hm?
[CHIO] There's not a
school in that alleyway.
Which leaves only one
destination, and that's...
[BOTH]
Sexy-time Central.
I'm gonna go watch.
Slow your roll, perv!
Let me have this, Chio.
I've gone my whole life
never knowing what
that world is like.
Also...
...think of all the dirt we'll
have on them after today.
Gossip makes you popular,
and this is my
ticket to the top!
[CHIO]
Wow, what a tool!
Manana, hold on.
I'm coming with you.
I mean, I guess it
would be nice of us
to warn them that someone saw.
If it were me, I'd rather
be busted by a student
than have a teacher
call my parents.
[MANANA sighs]
She is milking that one hard.
She expects me to believe
that this is about being
a good classmate and not
her own filthy curiosity?
What a little shit.
[MANANA]
Thanks, buddy!
[CHIO]
Sneak attack, go!
I've confirmed their location.
[CHIO] Let's see. It says
they're at an intersection
two blocks down,
but I have a feeling
they're further ahead.
Ya-hoo!
[MANANA]
We are on the case!
[CHIO] Sorry, Hosokawa,
but stalking you is so much fun!
What happened to your
struggle with morality?
[YUKI]
I'm sorry!
I swear it's not you, it's me.
I don't wanna date
anyone right now
so I can focus on track.
[CHIO gasps]
[CHIO] They weren't a couple.
He was asking her out.
You know how much
I love running.
Of course, I do.
I really appreciate you
being honest with me.
I hope this isn't too selfish.
But I do love
hanging out with you
and would like us
to stay friends.
And could you still help me
with my math homework sometimes?
Sure, no problem!
Then is it still cool if I
keep going to your marathons
so I can meet your hot friends?
And you have so many,
it's almost suspicious!
You're a real babe
magnet. Like a puppy!
I see! You weren't
even into me at all!
Wow. That's the most fun
I've ever seen anyone have
while getting rejected.
I swear she's ama...
About that, though,
I've been trying
to surround myself
with a different
kind of crowd lately.
One less superficial.
I wantna be friends
with this girl, Miyamo.
She's in my class.
The one with the glasses?
We walk to school
together sometimes...
[CHIO] Holy crap,
she's talking about me!
[HARUKI]
Oh, nice!
[MANANA]
Wait, what?
So you've been friends with
Hosokawa this whole time
and just forgot
to mention it to me?
No, that's not it. She just...
We walk to school
together sometimes.
It's really no big deal.
Yeah, I heard her say that,
and it is a big deal, so talk!
Um, okay.
I threw myself in the garbage
and then we walked to school...
[MANANA]
I see how it is!
I'm the comfort zone friend
until Hosokawa fully accepts you
into the pretty,
popular girl ring, right?
[CHIO]
That's not... Uh...
Manana, shut up!
Can you have a psycho
breakdown later?
Worst timing ever!
[BOTH gasp]
[YUKI]
Oh, my gosh.
Shh.
[gasping]
Whoa, that was so close!
You think they saw us?
Also, how do people breathe
when they're kissing?
Their mouths are
usually fully covered!
Our lips didn't
actually touch, right?
I mean, we were
just standing there.
I don't think so.
Stop blushing.
You're creepin' me out!
[MANANA] What is the matter
with you? That hurt!
[CHIO chuckling]
Hey, Chio! Get some
sleep last night?
Morning, Miyamo! How are you?
[gasps] It's too early in the
morning for this weirdness!
In what dimension do you ever
hang out with Hosokawa?
In all of them!
I was waiting for you, goober,
and she was passing by
on her way to school.
Hi. You're popular.
Good morning! I recognize you!
You're Miyamo's friend, right?
Uh, maybe?
Great! Is it okay if I
wait here with you, then?
Heck, yeah!
--Thank you! My name's Hosokawa.
--[YUKI] That was it.
And now we're walkin'
to school together.
I mean, is she even real?
She's nice to everyone!
[giggles] Girl!
[ALL laughing]
[CHIO]
It's not a dream.
We're actually all
walking together!
[MANANA]
Hey, Hosokawa,
now that we're
like quasi-friends,
can I ask you a question?
Sure! You can ask me
anything you want!
[MANANA]
Okay! Are you a virgin?
Uh...
[screaming]
Damage control! Shut your face!
Why would you ask her that?
Well, um, I've never actually
had a boyfriend before, so...
What?
Impossible. You're so popular!
Someone even told me that
Haruki guy asked you out!
Already?
It was just yesterday.
That was fast.
[CHIO] You're the one spreading
it around, you liar!
[clears throat]
Okay, so you know
I haven't done it,
but were you asking
because you have?
[BOTH]
Of course not! Just look at her!
[laughs]
Really? Then have you
ever been kissed before?
[CHIO]
That's a no. A solid no.
We agreed that our
lips never touched.
It was just awkward standing.
Yeah, I have.
It was just awkward standing!
It was this hot
college guy I met
when I was still
in middle school.
You started early!
Look at you go!
I grew up fast. We met online,
of course. Like you do.
[CHIO]
What?!
And she never
told me about this?
I thought we were friends.
Something's weird.
It's like she's
a different person.
Is she ignoring me because
of my online V-card?
You can basically
have an entire society
with just three people.
I'm definitely the central
being in our group,
the one they both
have in common.
I figured that would
give me the ability
to shape our dynamic.
Hey! What adventures do you
think I should have today?
[YUKI] I believe it's time
for you to do your homework.
Yeah, I don't wanna.
[YUKI] Surely you've heard
that youthful pursuits
become lifelong habits.
No one says that.
It's from Heroides .
It's the book of poems by Ovid.
[YUKI]
Oh-ho.
Might I presume you're
well-versed in literature?
Before my fall,
I majored in Latin
and read several
other languages.
[YUKI]
Oh, I see.
How about Metamorphoses ?
Yes, I know it.
Icarus was my favorite.
--And Narcissus ?
--[cries] Stop it!
[CHIO] I don't understand
what you're saying!
--These grapes are yummy!
--[YUKI] What about Shakespeare?
[CHIO]
Manana?
I could show you how to
do it if you want me to.
[CHIO]
Oh! I get it now!
She's just been using
me this whole time
to get close to Hosokawa!
I should've seen the signs!
Red flags were flying!
She betrayed me!
Curse you, you ungrateful slave!
[MANANA] I'm glad you
finally see it, Chio.
You were an excellent boost
on my way up the social ladder.
Now all I have to do
is use my connection
to my bestie, Hosokawa,
and join forces with all
the elites at our school.
I doubt you and I will ever
speak to each other again,
but I did enjoy
our time together.
Goodbye, Chio. Much love.
I'm impressed. You've already
done so much, Nonomura!
I was pretty advanced for
my age. Cried a lot of tears.
But at least now I know
how to pick a man.
Like, for example,
that guy over there,
He'll probably work some
blue-collar job all his life
--and never go anywhere.
--[YUKI] You think?
You should never trust
a man who has no idea
how the rest of
society views him...
--Morning, Yuki. How are you?
--Morning. Nice to see you!
Uh... Wha...?
Well, I don't mean to interrupt.
I just wanted to say hi.
I'd like you to meet
my friend, Ushida.
His office is just down
the street from our school!
Hi. Yuki's my running coach.
She's been whipping
me into shape.
[MANANA] Does she know
everyone on the planet?
[USHIDA] She came up and
talked to me one night
as I was out for a jog.
Excuse me.
The way you're landing is
hard on your knees. Watch.
[USHIDA]
She teaches me something new
every time we run
into each other.
Turns out real running shoes...
[MANANA]
So he's dressing that way
because Hosokawa told him to?
--[YUKI] ...to the office again?
--Yep.
--[MANANA] "President"?!
--Can't be president of a
company and not set
an example, right?
But I do feel bad for them.
I usually wipe off
the sweat and go in.
I'm thinking of adding showers
to the office, though.
No way.
Is that really you?
I remember when you used to be
in the normie group with me!
Oh, no! I'm so sorry! I didn't
mean to creep you out!
I know you're
allergic to my kind.
I've never seen
anything like it!
Step away! Your face
is blinding me.
I've been trapped in the
prison of your great beauty!
Gosh, you elites
sure are gorgeous!
I mean, flawless!
You're practically airbrushed!
You must go to a lot
of cool parties
'cause you're cool!
Oh, I almost forgot, bitch!
Tell me again, bitch,
about middle school, bitch.
And how you kissed a college guy
'cause you're so advanced!
Bitch, bitch. I wanna
learn from you, bitch!
Make me cool!
It was a lie!
I made it all up.
I never kissed a college guy
in middle school, or ever.
I just read that story in
a magazine, and went with it.
I see.
Well, thank goodness.
I'm glad some perv who seduced
a middle schooler online
wasn't your first kiss.
You deserve so much
better than that.
Thank you.
[CHIO]
Welcome back.
I've missed you.
[BOTH giggle]
[MANANA] Turns out that
old guy I made fun of
is kind of a big deal.
[CHIO]
Yeah, I heard.
But he looks more like
a grunt than the prez.
I know, right?
[MANANA] Just saying,
if I were some old dude
and hot Hosokawa ran up
to me in short shorts
asking about my job,
my brain would melt.
Uh! Yeah, I have a great job!
I'm a...
I'm the president of a company
right by your school!
[BOTH]
It all makes sense now.
Excuse us!
We heard you were the
president of a major company!
Could we ask you some questions
about what your job is like?
You have to forgive
my weird friend.
--She loves economics.
--[YUKI] I'd absolutely die
if you had a business card.
Don't you want to know
about his job, Hosokawa?
Sure.
[USHIDA]
I was lying about everything!
I'm sorry!
I'm just a blue-collar guy
who'll never go anywhere,
and I was trying to be cool!
It's fine! We totes get it!
You know, there are some women
who'll read about
other people's romances
and say it happened to them.
--[MANANA] Shut up.
--Everyone tells fibs!
You know, there are still times
when I don't feel like running
and I'll say I'm sick
to get out of it.
Ushida, the most important thing
I know about you is true.
The distance you've been
running has improved a lot!
So whenever we feel bad,
we should just go for a run!
[CHIO]
Uh, where are we going?
And do we have to run there?
[CHIO] I thought Hosokawa
only cared about running.
But there was more
to her than that.
It turns out we were having fun.
Plus, I got a sense of what
she really liked about it
and realized what others think
of you isn't always right.
Huh?
[ALL laughing]
Huh, they're not supposed
to be running around
in the street like that.
But look how happy
it makes them.
Who the hell is that old guy?!
[MANANA] Next time on
Chio's School Road !
"Bloody Butterfly Effect Two"
and "The Kabaddic Four"!
Looking forward
to seeing you there!
It's gonna be awesome!