[CHIO]
On mornings when I can leave
a little earlier than usual,
I take a stroll
through the park.
There are so many
interesting people around.
[CHIO]
Hm.
--Who parks like that?
--[chattering]
Motorcycle gang. Figures.
What is there to scream
about at this time of day?
So much for a
peaceful stroll. Gah!
Oh, well. This park's big
enough that I can avoid them.
[ANDOU] It was a real deal,
man. I wouldn't lie to ya.
[CHIO]
Brain fart.
What do I have for
first period again?
[ANDOU]
The name was Bloody Butterfly.
No.
[BIKER 3A]
What? Bloody Butterfly?
That's not a name, bro.
[ANDOU]
Damn straight it is.
It's hers. Had me on the
ground in a single blow.
[BIKERS]
Wait. A woman?
[CHIO] Oh, come on!
What's he doing here?!
[ANDOU] That's the reason
I can't stay with you.
I promised Bloody Butterfly
that I'd give up this life
if she'd let me live.
[BIKER 3A]
And that's it?
[ANDO]
I gave her my word.
[CHIO]
Huh? What the crap?
He took me seriously?
How is that even part of
a normal thought process?
[ANDOU]
At first, I thought it was
just some psycho
pickin' a fight.
But then there she was,
smirking like she just
swallowed my soul.
And that was it.
Next thing I know,
I'm trashed on the ground.
That's wicked.
But you're the Demon God.
No one scares you.
[BIKER 3B]
No one except Bloody Butterfly!
[BIKER 3C]
Crazy. Why haven't I ever heard
of this Bloody Butterfly chick?
[BIKER 3A]
I'll bet Bloody Butterfly
is from some underground turf.
[BIKER 3B]
"Bloody Butterfly."
Is it 'cause she kills people
with a butterfly knife?
[CHIO]
Stop saying it!
It's an online handle that is
meant to be seen, not heard!
Of course it sounds stupid
when you say it out loud!
Can I get a pronoun up in here?
Quit repeating it like that!
I can't take it anymore!
That's enough. Some things
aren't meant to be understood.
Bloody Butterfly is a creature
of the societal underworld.
Have some respect.
I learned a lot that day.
After speaking with
Bloody Butterfly,
I finally realized that
we were wasting our lives
with this child's play.
[screaming]
I didn't think it was possible,
but I'm glad to know.
Women like Bloody Butterfly
do exist in the world.
[screaming]
Someone so seemingly innocent,
out fighting terrorists,
surviving gang wars...
Bloody Butterfly does it all.
I'm just impressed that there's
someone who impresses you.
--Shit's wild.
--[BIKER 3D] Bull.
This is way too good to be true!
I need to see this
Bloody Butterfly myself!
--Take me to her!
--[ANDOU] You dumbass!
Are you saying you
don't trust my word?
[CHIO groaning]
This cannot be happening.
They need to shut up or
everyone will know who I am!
Look, you're the most
badass guy I know.
That's why we gotta meet her.
Even if it means I
drag her here myself.
I'll help.
She must know some kind of
underground martial arts BS.
Otherwise, how would
anyone beat you?
[BIKER 3D]
Then it's settled!
We do everything in our power
to find her and learn her trade!
[ALL] Let the hunt for
Bloody Butterfly begin!
[BIKER 3D]
What's the matter? Are you okay?
Don't move! Don't say
a word. Don't breathe.
Don't turn around.
Um... How the...
Where'd you come from?
Bloody Butterfly?
[BIKERS]
What? Oh, no!
Bloody... Butterfly!
Wait. That's Bloody Butterfly?
But she's just a kid...
with glasses.
[BIKER 3D] I thought she'd
be all leather suited
with blades and shit.
[CHIO sighs] Well, of course
they're gonna be disappointed
after he built me up like that.
At least it makes what I have
to say more believable.
You here for me,
Bloody Butterfly?
You guessed it.
You and I need to
have a little chat.
But not here. I wanna
speak to you alone.
[ANDOU whimpers]
[ANDOU] You guys stay put!
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
[ANDOU]
None of your business!
'Kay. I'm listening. What is it?
I already told you
I'm leaving the gang.
--[ANDOU] I just had to--
--Uh, that's not...
[ANDOU gasps]
I get it now.
Right. You're here to
drag me down with you!
Sorta...
Oh, I'm afraid I may
have misled you somehow.
I've never even held a gun.
--Much less killed anyone.
--[CHIO] Yeah, I know! I get it!
[ANDOU] I don't think I could
handle the guilt of--
Hey! What I'm
saying is, me, too!
It's all just a big silly lie.
[CHIO]
That is a reasonable reaction!
So, get this...
There's no underground
organization,
no killings, no terrorists.
I'm just your average
high school kid.
More like, below average.
[chuckles]
[CHIO] No, you can't
laugh! I'm not joking!
I was freaked out after burning
my leg on your muffler thing!
Remember when I told
you about guys
being crippled for life?
I was talking about gamer nerds
being hooked on gaming!
That's "the life"
I was describing!
[CHIO]
The face of disappointment.
But I don't regret
clearing this up.
It needed to happen.
And I'm glad he
eventually believed me
even though believing me is
what got us into this mess
in the first place.
Okay. Let's get this straight.
[CHIO]
Yes, let's.
You're sayin' you're
just a normal kid,
and you were making
your way to school
when some hoodlum was
gettin' in your face.
You were able to ward him off
with your talent for lying
and a little bit of dumb luck.
Then you decided to scare
the crap out of him
and make him quit his gang.
And then this dumb
idiot trusted you.
He went around tellin'
his friends about these lies
as if they were true.
[screams]
And now he looks like
a pathetic joke.
Is that what you just told me?
[CHIO]
Holy crap.
He's totally going
to headbutt me!
I can't move!
That's hilarious!
[CHIO]
Huh?
[ANDOU laughing]
Frickin' genius.
I don't even know what to say.
[laughing]
[ANDOU] Oh, man, I hope
they didn't hear me.
This whole damn time,
you were just a
normal nerdy kid.
Exactly how you look.
[laughs] Ridiculous.
Man, I guess knowing that
explains why that name
of yours is so lame.
"Bloody Butterfly." [laughs]
I actually said that name
out loud with a straight face!
"Bloody Butterfly." [laughing]
Can we not talk about it?
The point of this awkward convo
is that I don't want
it to spread anymore.
[ANDOU]
I know, I know!
Well, if I fell for that,
I have no regrets
about quitting.
Man, you totally got me!
It's their turn.
Let's see this through
to the bitter end.
Come on. We're headin' back.
[CHIO]
"We," as in you and me?
[ANDOU] It'll be fun.
Just follow my lead.
Should we check on him?
It's been awhile.
[BIKER 3B] Nah, he's fine.
Andou can handle himself.
--[ANDOU screaming]
--[ALL gasp]
[BIKERS]
What happened?
Go! Now! Bloody
Butterfly got me!
She's dangerous!
Go save yourselves!
Andou, look at me.
Oh, shit!
This is it! She's gonna
kill all of us!
She's a monster!
[CHIO]
Slower. Walk slower.
She's totally unarmed.
She beat his ass
with pure strength!
Damn. Looks like
we're all screwed!
[ANDOU yelps]
Butterflies!
That's the sign she gives
when she's about to use
her special attack!
Soon everyone for miles
will be bloodied,
or dead, or something.
This is the end!
Here she goes! Run!
[screaming]
You must erase her
from your mind
and tell no one of this day!
Don't try to provoke her!
What are you doing? Run!
I will not run!
I will end you, Bloody
Butterfly, you hear me?
Andou, you're my friend, and
I'm willing to die for you!
I told you to run!
Go or I'll kill you!
[BIKER 3D screaming]
[ANDOU]
Well, that should do it.
Did ya see the looks
on their faces?
What cowards.
Look at this.
They call themselves
a biker gang,
and they ran away on foot.
Um, thank you for the adventure!
[ANDOU]
Hm?
Here. This is for your face.
[ANDOU]
No way.
If I take that, things'll
only get more complicated.
See ya, Bloody Butterfly!
Dude, you have to
stop calling me that!
Hey, do you remember that time
I told you about
some skanky girl
who came to school
on the back of a bike
with a motorcycle gangster?
Uh... I mean, barely.
Okay, you're not
allowed to ask how,
but I totally know
who this girl is!
I've never seen her around,
but she calls herself
"Bloody Butts and Thighs"
or something.
Or maybe it was "Butterfly,"
that sounds familiar.
Huh?
I'm having gaming flashbacks
for some reason. Hm...
[CHIO]
Um, I used to play you
under that name
all the time, dummy.
Does it ring any bells for you?
Not even a little bit.
[CHIO] That settles it.
She's the next to go.
[CHIO]
Chio's School Road !
He said my handle was lame?
Let's see how great
his gang's name is!
Found 'em!
He didn't even try
to make it intimidating.
It's actually really cute!
[CHIO grunting, yelling]
Hey, Manana, be a pal and stick
your arm out real quick.
Hell no!
[CHIO]
Rude!
I wanna see if I'm doing
all my CQC moves correctly.
Oh, okay, let me just
sacrifice my limbs for you.
If this is about a video game,
you need an intervention.
Man, you don't even know.
That action is awesome!
You wouldn't believe how
good the cut scenes are.
Damn, you're really wasting your
life away with that crap, huh?
Who hurt you?
[CHIO]
Check me out!
Face block! Punch!
Roundhouse! Block!
He's comin' from the left.
[MANANA] You just look like
you're really determined
to kill flies. It's so...
[CHIO]
And... twist!
Give me the password
to the secret pics
hidden on your computer,
and the arm lives.
Bite me, you're insane!
Just break it!
I hope there's some entity
you praise nightly
for giving you these
athletic skills
you don't deserve.
Aw, crap, that reminds me.
Our fitness test is tomorrow.
I'm guessing you haven't
prepped for it?
Fake it till you make it, bruh.
Chio, you're actually athletic
and in a sports club.
It doesn't make sense for you
to keep blowing
these things off.
Yeah, it does! Once they
know your true skills,
they start forcing you into
sports festivals and tournaments
and I'm not about that!
I like being a nobody.
It's peaceful, okay?
I forgot, you're the
patron saint of lame-o's.
If some sports star messes up,
the whole country knows.
If I mess up, shoulders shrug.
Fine, you wanna work that
fitness, girl? Come on.
Let's see how many of these
side squat jumps you can do
without looking ridiculous!
--Fight me!
--[MANANA] Not yet.
I'd like to go back to
the part where you said
"work that fitness" as if
it's your everyday lingo.
Hurry up! Fast as you can!
Like some crab waitin'
in line to pee!
I dare you to do it faster.
Check it out! Can't even see me!
Oh, my god! Do that and say
"kabaddi!" really fast.
--Kabaddi, kabaddi, kabaddi!
--[MANANA laughing]
I can't! You look just
like those weirdos!
You're even making
the face they make!
I think I broke my ribs!
I had no idea you loved kabaddi!
--And you know all the moves!
--[CHIO] I didn't even know
it was a real thing before...
Good morning! Did I hear
you mention kabaddi?
Have I got a surprise for you!
[CHIO, MANANA]
Huh? What is it?
A kabaddi expert!
[MADOKA]
Hi there. I'm Kushitori Madoka.
Captain of the Kabaddi Club.
Nice to meet you both.
[BOTH]
Wait, it's a real club?
Shit.
[MADOKA] So you wanna
know how to play, huh?
Want to learn all the moves?
That's what it sounded like.
Isn't this so exciting?
[BOTH] We, uh...
We're sorry about that.
But why?
It's not like you were
making fun of it, right?
[BOTH]
Right!
[MADOKA]
You just admire the sport
and were praising the athletes.
Uh, yeah.
[MADOKA] You were trying
to figure out the rules
so you could play one day.
[BOTH]
Yep.
Great! Well, I'm more than
happy to teach you both!
We'll have more room over here.
Isn't this fun?
[CHIO] Sure, if FUN
stands for F'd Up Nonsense!
Kabaddi, kabaddi, kabaddi,
kabaddi, kabaddi, kabaddi,
kabaddi, kabaddi!
If you're in the
raider position,
you keep yelling "kabaddi"
while in the enemy circle.
[CHIO]
Wait, they actually say that?
And here I thought
that was just a joke.
[MADOKA] The object is to
touch your opponents
and run back to your side.
Once on your base,
you get points for everyone you
touched on the opposite team,
and the ones who were touched,
of course, are then out.
Got it! So everyone takes
turns being a raider,
and whoever isn't a raider
has to avoid getting
touched, kinda like tag?
[MADOKA]
Correct.
[CHIO]
Wow, I so totally don't care!
How is this my life?
"Sorry I'm late. I was
forced into kabaddi lessons
against my will!"
I wish she'd just let us go!
I got stuff to do!
[MADOKA]
The biggest difference, though,
is the defense has
a way of scoring, too.
If you're on defense,
try to tackle and capture
the raider like this.
Your team gets the point
if you completely stop
their movement in their tracks.
It sounds like a lot,
but just remember:
raiders touch, defense catches.
Well, I sure learned
a lot today!
Me, too! This was great!
Good to hear! Now let's play!
If you lose, you join
the club. Deal?
Sweet! That'll help us out
'cause, once all the
third years graduate,
the club will be
short on members.
You have no idea
how stoked I was
when I heard some first years
were so interested in the game!
Well, define "interested."
--Unless...
--[CHIO] So close.
...there's been
a misunderstanding.
I asked before if you were
making fun of my sport
and you said no.
Is that still true?
[CHIO]
I get it.
This was revenge
by guilt-splaining.
She wants to prove
it's not a joke sport.
Ugh! If she wasn't a
third year, I'd be out.
But I can't risk being
noticed by haters.
Fine. Let's hurry
and get it over with.
All right, you two
are the raiders!
I chose you, Manana!
Wh-Why me?
'Cause you're so good at it!
Uh... A-hem.
Kab-kabaddi. Kab-kabaddi.
[MADOKA]
Just touch them and turn back.
As soon as you stop struggling,
I can let you go.
[CHIO]
Hold the phone!
This is not what
she described earlier!
This is good! Keep
trying to get away.
We'll continue to hold you
down until you give up.
I give up! Get off!
[CHIO]
She is not messing around!
[GAME ANNOUNCER]
Manana is out!
So, there's no rush or anything,
but you never said how we're
supposed to end this game.
That's a very good question.
Usually, it's timed
and players go out and
back in until it ends.
But we all have to get
to school eventually,
so I think we should just play
until one side is
completely eliminated.
[CHIO] Huh?! Wait!
Now it's them against me,
and if I get jumped, we lose?
I wanna be the raider
for our team next!
[CHIO] So if Hosokawa touches
me and then blasts off,
we become members
of Awkward Tag Club?
I guess I'll try to catch her,
but I have to be cautious
or she'll end up touching me
when I'm not expecting it.
Whoa. "Touching me when
I'm not expecting it."
Kabaddi's deep!
I think I'm having
an "a-ha" moment.
Being in a club
no one knows exists
instead of the Tennis Club
might make my school life
frickin' magical.
[CLASSMATE 4A]
It's nice to meet you!
[CLASSMATE 4B] I love the
first day of class! Don't you?
What clubs are you in
this year, Miyamo?
Oh, I'm in the Kabaddi Club!
--Kaba...
--D?
[CLASSMATE 4C]
Awesome! Kabaddi, kabaddi!
--Oh, no, I'm scared!
--[CLASSMATE 4C] Tackle!
[laughing]
--You got me!
--[CLASSMATE 4C] I win...
Stop making fun of kabaddi!
Also, the one who chants
is the raider, idiot!
You don't chant when you
tackle someone! That's defense!
Um, he didn't mean it?
[CLASSMATE 4C]
Out of my face, freak.
[CHIO]
That's a big old nope!
I don't need the drama!
Impressive. Looks like she's
actually got some skills.
[gasping] I'm out of breath.
[CHIO] Ugh! No clue
how I got past her.
Does that mean I'm
the raider now?
What kind of animals
can handle this?
My stamina bar's depleted.
But I must not let
this become my fate.
[MADOKA]
What the...?
[CHIO] My below-average life
depends on me taking this
weird, violent playground
game spin-off seriously.
But it's so hard.
Game brain, activate!
I'll treat kabaddi like a
PvP game and bust some ass!
And now, everyone I touch
will turn into ticking bombs.
My mission, turn both
enemies into said bombs
and then escape
before they explode.
If captured, I'll be
tortured and killed!
I'll need to perform a spell
in order to activate
my special ability.
Kabaddi.
[CHIO]
Yes! It's working!
Kabaddi, kabaddi...
[MADOKA]
Careful, Yuki! Stay close.
Something's changed.
I don't trust that girl.
[CHIO]
Kabaddi, kabaddi, kabaddi!
[gasps]
[MADOKA] Her strong skills
don't hide the fact
that she's still a noob.
She's too deep in our territory!
Even if she manages to touch us,
there's no way she'll be able
to escape once we capture her!
I've got her back!
Now! Run, Yuki! Tackle her
'Kay!
[CHIO]
When the enemy grabs you, twist!
It'll throw them off balance
and give you an advantage!
Nice move, but I'm
not letting go!
[CHIO] Naturally, she's coming
straight for me with no tact.
Kabaddi!
I got a move for
that, too, biyotch!
Switch!
[YUKI yelps]
[gasping]
Um, does this mean she won?
Um...
[YUKI]
Okay! I think Miyamo's leaving!
Uh...
So, Kushitori, can
you move your hand?
[CHIO]
Mission complete.
I tagged you both
and made it back.
I win. I'm outta here.
[MADOKA] No. First tell
me how you did that.
So, um, about your hand?
I saw the twinkle in your eye
when you attacked Manana.
I recognized it and used
it to my advantage.
You're a sucker for the ladies.
Nothin' wrong with that.
And then, when
Hosokawa was raiding,
you got completely distracted
looking up her skirt.
I wish you could've seen your
face. Full-on pervy smirk.
[YUKI]
Wait, what?
So I knew what to do
when you grabbed me.
I twisted your hand toward
her perineum, and you froze,
allowing me to make
my final escape.
I guess you could call
that a win-win sitch.
Also, you should just be real.
You don't have to pretend to
like kabaddi to wrestle girls!
[MADOKA] You don't know what
you're talking about, Miyamo!
I love this sport, okay?
Nothing and no one else moves
me the way kabaddi does!
You take it back!
If you can remove your
arm from her crotch
and play another round.
[YUKI whimpering]
[MADOKA]
I can't!
Just thinking about
accidentally groping her again
is making my body
totally tense up!
I can't! I can't move!
[YUKI] Kushitori, please,
you're grabbing my butt!
[MADOKA]
I admit defeat. I lose.
Please let go of me!
It's starting to get weird!
[MADOKA]
I guess I should thank you.
You helped me realize
how unprepared I was
as a kabaddist today.
And, sorry for, you know,
the other things that happened.
Eh. No big!
Hi. Since we're kinda friends,
can I please ask you a question?
Sure.
How can I get my jugs
to be as big as yours are?
[CHIO] Of course.
Of course she would choose
to ask something completely
random and horrifying.
That girl is sick in the head.
[MADOKA] Actually, I was
just thinking about that.
It's strange.
I wasn't always like this.
I had a normal body until
I started playing kabaddi.
You think that's related?
[MADOKA]
If you didn't know,
Kabaddi originated
over in India.
I read somewhere that
a lot of the moves
were created with
yoga as a basis.
I think that's it, because
of the yoga involved,
my body started changing in ways
I never could've imagined.
[CHIO, MANANA]
Kabaddi, kabaddi, kabaddi...
[whistle blows]
[MADOKA]
Chio's School Road !
I want more.
I must devote myself to the
ways of kabaddi even more!
For it let me touch Yuki's butt!
[CHIO, MANANA]
Kabaddi, kabaddi, kabaddi...
[MADOKA laughing]
[YUKI] Next time on
Chio's School Road ,
"Smoke on a Sailor,"
"Taking the Cherry
Blossom in Your Hand,"
and "Manana's School Road"!
Looking forward to it! Kabaddi!