[CHIO]
I gotta pee.
Like, now.
Stay in. Please don't burst.
[CHIO]
This is your fault, Chio.
A of all, why go to the city
to find an open restroom?
B of all, there's no
excuse for drinking tea
on the way to school!
It's not even hot!
[panting]
[CHIO]
Attagirl. Focus. Hold it in.
[panting]
[CHIO groans]
I can't move!
[heartbeats]
[CHIO]
No!
I can't do it!
[CHIO yelps]
Please stay in there!
[panting]
[CHIO]
My limit's been reached!
I'm chipping away
at my S-A-N points
with every step I take!
[NARRATOR] Shit, I need
to go. Anzai- sensei . Now.
[CHIO]
Screw restrooms.
At this point, I'll squat
behind a dumpster.
[CAT meows]
[CHIO]
You and your privileged life.
Must be nice having
the whole world
as your personal toilet!
[CHIO]
What's in there?
I'm putting everything I have...
[CHIO]
...into this moment!
Oh, sweet, sweet salvation!
I'm in love with whoever
put a restroom here.
Thank you for your mercy!
[growling]
Mother of god, this dam's
about to burst open!
Almost there! Almost there!
I can make it!
[birds chirping]
[laughs]
[CHIO] If there's a bladder
deity, I believe in you!
That was so close.
Though, if I needed
an emergency squat,
this bottle would've
done the trick.
I could've even carried
it with me to school.
It would almost be
the right color.
But... thank goodness
it didn't come to that!
New mission.
Find a way out of
the men's restroom
without being seen.
They can't judge me!
I had to go!
What was I supposed to do,
lift my leg on a lamp post?
It was the closest one!
Oh, come on! Why now?
Right next to me? Really?
[MAN screaming]
[CHIO] If this is a nightmare,
I need to wake up!
What is happening?
I don't wanna know!
Please don't ever
let me find out!
I feel so violated!
[MAN]
Whew.
That was a doozy of a toozy.
I gotta go before I suffocate.
What if someone walks
in as I'm leaving?
I know what to do.
[CHIO] I must open the
chakra of my third eye.
Providing intuition
and creating a bridge
to the outside world!
[CHIO]
And a Wall Hack!
[NARRATOR]
The Wall Hack!
This is a cheat some players
use in online games
to reveal the exact location
of enemy combatants
behind walls.
All clear!
[CHIO] See ya never,
gross Man-Turd Bank!
[MAN 5B] Damn it! Can I have
one day without hair sweat?
♪ I've got the Sweaty
Hair Day blues ♪
♪ And I'm cryin' just tryin'
to be so smooth ♪
[CHIO] You've failed me,
chakra intuition.
I'll have to think
of another plan.
I noticed something
when I first got here.
There was a bus stop
right in front of the door.
And where there's a bus stop,
there are swarms of people
hanging around the sidewalk.
It's a miracle I made it
here without being seen!
But that means my only
way out has been vetoed.
[CHIO]
Crap.
[CHIO] I guess I ran into
the storage closet.
I thought the smell
of cleaning products
was too good to be true.
[CHIO] I mean, that's how
an assassin would handle it.
"This hose'll work."
But I might go to prison.
Would it be worth it
to guard my purity?
Chio, shut up! That's stupid!
There's probably something
else in here I can use.
[CHIO]
What are those?
I've never seen them
in the girls' room before.
Weird. [gasps]
[CHIO]
But they're perfect.
They'll be the key
to my great escape!
I just need to
buy a little time.
[MAN 5B] ♪ Who's that guy
lookin' oh so fly? ♪
♪ Yeah, that's me ♪
[CHIO]
Do me a favor, sign.
Stay here and don't move!
All right. My exit
is the other way!
Hark!
What is this light shining
into my eyes? Is it hope?
Freedom awaits!
[CHIO]
Sha-bam! There are definitely
fewer people walking
on this side.
[CHIO]
But it's not go-time, yet.
This doesn't look good.
[MAN]
Oh!
Ah, cleaning? Not today.
I'm about to erupt!
Excuse me?
Sorry, but I've
got an emergency!
I'm coming in!
I don't usually do this!
[CHIO]
Man Trap, activate!
Oh, god! What the hell?
There's pee-pee everywhere!
What is wrong with people?
Uh, I'll find a tree!
Try not to breathe!
[CHIO]
Time successfully obtained!
Green tea, you're forgiven
for torturing my insides.
Sorry whoever has
to clean this up!
Okay. How are we doin' out here?
This is perfect!
Two girls in miniskirts
surrounded by old guys!
And go!
Good things come
to those who stall!
If my calculations are correct,
he's on the other
side of that wall.
Fly!
[CHIO]
Random mysterious ball
brought to you by the
magical storage closet!
Huh?
Whoa! They couldn't make it
another five feet? Disgusting!
[CHIO]
Firing all rounds!
[CAT purrs]
They were only 100 yen,
can you believe it?
[GIRL 5A]
Aw. Hi, little kitty!
[GIRL 5B]
He's so cute!
[GIRL 5A] We should take a video
and post it on the internet!
[GIRL 5B]
Yes! Make sure you tag me!
[GIRL 5A] Uh, duh! I'm gonna
tag everyone in our class!
Who's a baby?
[CHIO]
Perv-Lock blind spot.
Achieved!
Cross-check complete.
Prepare for launch.
And liftoff!
[GIRL 5A]
Yes! Just keep doing that.
[MEN] Just keep doing
that. Keep doing that.
Stay right there!
[CHIO grunting]
What? No! Why? Not now!
[CHIO]
Am I fat all of a sudden?
Freedom!
[CHIO screams]
[GIRL 5A]
Are you okay?
You scared the crap out of us.
I thought you were like
an alien or something.
No human can travel that fast.
Do you need help?
[GIRL 5A] Can you tell us
where you came from?
[CHIO] George! I found you,
you furry little bandit!
I was so worried, I freaked
out when I saw you!
That's right. I had
to jump so high.
I dove into the air to squeeze
your precious little face!
[CAT meows]
No, George! We're not done yet!
At least let me thank you!
Only aliens would ever
love cats that much.
I love cats, too.
I wonder why these cat balls
smell so good.
Yeah it smells kinda like
flowers, and olives?
Cats are so weird, aren't they?
[NARRATOR]
But it wasn't a cat toy.
[MAN 1] Wait. That looks like
one of those things
I see rolling around in urinals.
[MAN 2]
What are they doing with those?
[MAN 1] Just seeing it
makes me have to pee.
Good thing there's a restroom
right around the corner.
That's disgusting!
Who does this?
[MAN]
Chio's School Road!
I wish I knew what these were.
They came in handy today.
[GOTOU]
What do we have here?
You kids sensationalize
some new thing every year.
Be sure to leave your toys
at home from now on.
My name is Shinozuka Momo.
I'm the disciplinary monitor
of the Samejima Academy
student council.
Discipline at this school
is crumbling lately.
We've recently received
a number of disturbing calls
from people who live nearby
complaining about
our students' behavior.
The strangest part is,
according to the reports,
it seems all of the incidents
may have been caused
by one person.
Let's be more observant,
and report to me
if you see anything.
[SHINOZUKA]
This is my chance.
I can finally be of use
to Mr. Gotou!
[SHINOZUKA] I decided to take
a detour this morning
and investigate the area
where most of these incidents
are alleged to have happened.
So far, no issues.
It's actually peaceful.
Makes me wonder if these reports
really involved students
from our school.
Those two are a great example
of how our students typically
conduct themselves.
They're calm and graceful.
I'm so proud that
Samejima Academy
holds a standard
of high morality.
[CHIO, MANANA giggling]
[SHINOZUKA]
Oh! She's picking a flower.
I wonder if she's planning
to make a bookmark?
How fun!
[CHIO]
Whoop-a!
[MANANA]
Wanna try that again?
I double dare you!
[SHINOZUKA]
What's going on?
And why are they doing this?
I can't believe these girls
are from our school.
Oh, I'm real scared 'cause
you wrapped your root!
How the hell'd you do that?
[SHINOZUKA] They're just going
to act as if nothing happened?
Did that whip burn your ass?
Nope. Didn't feel it.
[SHINOZUKA]
I'll, um...
I'll need to investigate
this further.
[CHIO] Just like that.
It'll go way faster. Trust me.
--[MANANA] No, it won't.
--You're not even gonna try?
[SHINOZUKA]
Looks like they've stopped.
And now they're arguing?
Look, if you wanna do it,
fine. But I'm out.
[SHINOZUKA]
I can't really hear them, but...
You know, you're pushin' it.
[SHINOZUKA]
She makes her carry her bag?
[CHIO]
Guard that with your life!
[MANANA]
Yeah, bite me.
[SHINOZUKA] Wait a minute!
That's the parking lot
that connects at
the top of the hill.
No! Could she possibly be...
...trying to take
a shortcut to school?
Why? Why would she even
want to do that?
Is there some kind of
emergency this morning?
No, look!
It's much faster
to walk normally.
Exactly as expected!
But her friend is
just standing there.
She's not offering to help her!
How's it workin' out for ya?
[SHINOZUKA] Seriously.
What is she doing up there?
And more importantly,
these two girls...
Are they really even
friends at all?
It doesn't seem like it to me.
[CHIO panting]
[SHINOZUKA]
She took out some water.
Is she giving it to her friend?
[SHINOZUKA]
Evidently not!
Ah!
[SHINOZUKA]
It's just as I thought.
Okay, here.
[CHIO]
Manana!
[SHINOZUKA]
This is so beautiful!
She watered the flowers?
She chose the flowers
over her friendship.
Manana!
[SHINOZUKA]
I think she's lost it!
[CHIO] You'd let me die
of thirst? Seriously?
[SHINOZUKA] Now they're
back to fighting again.
How can they be students
of Samejima Academy?
[SHINOZUKA] Mr. Gotou
and the student council
should have been guiding them
and nurturing
their minds, but...
[SHINOZUKA sighs]
How unsightly.
I cannot restrain
myself any longer.
Both of you! Stop that at once!
[SHINOZUKA]
I'm the disciplinary monitor
of the Samejima Academy
student council.
Shinozuka Momo!
You have officially
been issued a warning!
You are hereby forbidden from
hanging out with each other!
Oh, snap, it's that girl.
Yeah, the one who's always
clinging to Mr. Gotou.
I realize it was rude of me,
but I've been following you two
for quite some time now.
I saw you beat your
friend with a whip.
You stood by and watched
as she climbed a wall.
Finally, you both
fought over water!
[BOTH yelp]
I'm doing you a favor!
You're horrible influences
on each other!
Listen well.
True friends lift each other up.
They seek righteousness!
They stick up for each other!
Friends face hardships with you.
They're the only ones
who will have your backs
in life or death situations!
[MANANA] Um, I take it you don't
really have any friends, do you?
Whoop, there it is.
Wait, what? How did
you know that?
Because it's only
those without friends
that believe a perfect
friendship could exist.
She's been my best friend
and pain in my butt
since grade school.
Oh, and PS: the whole reason
I even wanted to go to Samejima
is because I found out it was
where Chio was applying!
[CHIO] What the what?
I didn't know that!
All right, if that's the case,
then prove your friendship to me
in a way that I will understand!
If you fail to convince me,
I'll report every destructive
and dangerous activity
I witnessed today
to the student council!
Do I make myself clear?
Sure. You need the essence
of our friendship
to melt your heart, right?
Well, we can't risk
you dismissing
our ten years together
as false, can we?
[BOTH]
Most certainly not.
[CHIO, MANANA]
Prove our friendship? How?
[MANANA] Do we tell her
each other's birthdays?
No, you could find
anyone's birthday now.
The color of her undies?
Her stupid crushes?
No, those are all too easy.
[CHIO]
Manana.
[MANANA gasps]
It's time to do the thing.
[MANANA]
"The thing"?
Out here? We can't do
"the thing" out here--we'll die!
What other choice do we have?
[CHIO]
Watch, listen, and believe.
Back in grade school
gym class...
[MANANA] ...we pondered
the meaning of friendship
and used it to create...
[CHIO]
...this interpretive dance.
It's called...
[BOTH]
...Mananacchio.
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH meowing]
[BOTH]
Meow!
[BOTH] ♪ Meow, meow, meow,
meow, meow, meow. ♪
♪ Meow, meow, meow, meow. ♪
♪ Meowy, meowy.
Meow-meowy, meow, meowy. ♪
♪ Meow, meow, meow,
meow, meow, meow. ♪
♪ Meow, meow, meow, meow. ♪
♪ Meowy, meowy, meow-meowy.
Meow, meowy. ♪
♪ Purr, purr, purr, purr, purr,
purr, purr, purr, purr... ♪
[BOTH]
Meow.
[BOTH] ♪ Meow, meow, meow,
meow, meow, meow. ♪
♪ Meow, meow, meow, meow. ♪
BOTH] ♪ Meow, meow, meow,
meow, meow, meow, ♪
♪ Meow, meow,
meow-meow, meow... ♪
♪ I'm Meownana ♪
♪ And I'm Chiow ♪
[BOTH]
♪ Mananacchio! ♪
That's all we got.
Are you gonna say anything?
I'm just so moved by this.
[CHIO, MANANA]
She's bawling?
[SHINOZUKA]
I could see it.
I could see the
friendship very clearly.
You worked so hard
to build it! [crying]
I'll keep my promise
and not report anything.
--[MANANA] Okay, uh, thanks.
--[CHIO] Cool. Bye.
How long has it been since
we've actually done that?
[MANANA]
Don't talk about it.
Hold on! Can I ask you
one last question?
Well... Okay.
How do you get closer
to someone you know casually
that has become very
important to you?
[BOTH]
Hm?
This is totally about
Mr. Gotou, isn't it?
Huh?!
I'm gonna take that
as a "hell yes."
Relationships between
students and teachers
are greatly frowned upon!
[CHIO chuckles]
Yeah, they are.
[MANANA]
Here's the thing.
[SHINOZUKA]
Uh, okay?
[MANANA] Let's say there is
an issue with this pairing.
No one ever goes
after the student.
It's always about
the pervy teacher!
So, shimmy on out there
and pursue him
as hard as you can!
[CHIO]
Ay, ay, ay.
You can always bait
her with a scandal.
[MANANA]
Yeah!
You think it'll
work out? Really?
I'm counting on it!
[SHINOZUKA]
Okay.
Would it be all right
if I talked to you
about this again sometime?
--Duh!
--[SHINOZUKA] Thank you.
[MANANA] Make sure you keep
your rivals in check!
[SHINOZUKA]
What?
Yeah. And don't give away
too much too fast.
Be mysterious.
[SHINOZUKA]
Oh! Okay!
[CHIO] Pursue him hard
and be mysterious?
Is that possible?
[MANANA]
Yes, it's an art!
[SHINOZUKA]
Please teach me!
And that concludes my report.
You didn't see
any incidents? Huh.
Don't make a habit of
investigating things like this
on your own, all right?
[SHINOZUKA]
Yes, sir.
[GOTOU]
I have to say,
your face doesn't look
as tense as usual.
Something exciting happen
while you were out patrolling
you'd like to share?
Uh, I don't really know
how to answer that.
I'm supposed to
remain mysterious.
[GOTOU]
Hm?
It's a secret.
--[MANANA] Ooh, girl.
--[CHIO] Ooh!
[SHINOZUKA]
Chio's School Road !
Hello, there! Good morning!
[STUDENT 5F]
Aw, Mr. Gotou!
Can't you just
hear me out first?
Not when you approach
me like that.
[SHINOZUKA]
This is what Nonomura meant!
Make sure you keep
your rivals in check!
[SHINOZUKA]
Um, excuse me.
If you're going to
approach the adviser
of the disciplinary committee,
you need to dress
a bit more appropriately!
Oh?
--[SHINOZUKA gasps]
--I see what's going on.
But are you sure
that's what you want?
For me to look more
prim and proper?
It might make things
more difficult for you.
What would happen
if I did it better?
Well, I, uh...
[SHINOZUKA growls]
[GOTOU]
Huh?
[MANANA]
Next time on Chio's School Road.
"Everyone's Own Path"
and "Chio Eludes!"
Looking forward to...
♪ Meow, meow, meow,
meow, meow, meow. ♪
♪ Meow, meow, meow, meow. ♪