All right, real talk. You ever
think of a list of things
you wanna do before you die?
Because I totally have.
What kind of things?
Girl, I've put it out
into the universe
that I'll meet some
foreign hottie.
He'll be wandering around
town like a sexy lost lamb,
bump into me and
ask for directions.
I'll take his hand,
he'll pull me close and...
[CHIO]
Okay, I'm done with this story!
You love it!
Okay, now you tell me.
What do you wanna do?
'Kay! Mine's a good one!
You ever seen those jerks
who toss their cigarettes
out of car windows?
One day, I'm gonna pick one up.
I think you dropped this, bruh.
Then, I'll flick it
back in their car!
[MANANA]
Hm?
Chio, that's stupid
and doesn't count.
Oh, come on! It's so cool!
[MANANA] That's not something
you have to work toward.
It's one of those
things that you can do
when you're bored on your
way to school at any time.
Go do it to that lady.
[CHIO]
Hm, I don't know.
Oh, look. She's
got a phone call.
Thanks for getting back to me.
So, uh, I need you
to do something
about that part-timer.
I don't wanna see
him there on Monday.
[MANANA]
Chio, now's your chance!
Whoa!
Did she really just
catch that thing?
[CHIO]
Uh-oh.
[CHIO groans]
[CHIO]
I think I broke my clavicle!
I'm gonna be paralyzed for life!
She's getting away!
No, wait! Come back!
Let it go! It's not worth it!
Oh! My goodness!
Looks like you took
quite a tumble.
Yep! She's a train wreck.
[MANANA]
So, know what I learned today?
No matter how simple
something seems,
you'll find a way
to make it extreme.
[MANANA]
Wait, did you actually get hurt?
[CHIO]
Spiritually, yes.
And I missed my chance
to throw this in her car.
[gasps] You should probably
throw that thing away.
Why? It's not lit.
Besides, that lady
tossed it, right?
So I didn't steal it.
There's nothing wrong
with keeping it.
As long as I don't smoke it.
[MANANA] This is how
all those stories begin.
They say it was just a prop
to make them look cool,
and then they become
smokers for life.
There was that one time!
[CHIO] You can tell which
characters are cool
'cause they smoke.
[MAN]
Make my day.
[chuckles]
You know what?
You picked up
someone else's trash.
They were whizzing by
trying to ruin our planet,
and you protected our future.
You're a hero, Chio!
[camera clicking]
Yes! I love this lighting!
Give me duck-face!
Like this?
[MANANA]
Yas, Queen!
Just keep the cig away
from your mouth
so they can't say you smoked it!
Hold that look right there!
Hashtag hot-and-legal!
[shutter clicking]
So legal. Still legal.
Yas, legal!
[BOTH screaming]
--[MANANA] You're such a rebel!
--[CHIO] I'm such a rebel!
[CHIO]
How is that me?
I'm freaking out!
Look at my smirk!
I am fierce AF!
[MANANA]
Okay, full body shots! Go!
Oh, that's good! You're a
tiger! You're a socialite!
"Emo summer vacay!" Oh! Love it!
[MANANA] Ah! How is she cool
with me taking so many photos
that would ruin her life
if they got out?
Oh, my god, what if
they did get out?
I wanna post these so bad,
I can't stop drooling!
[MANANA]
Give me Brooding Assassin!
You just burned down your
husband's mistress's house
with him still in it!
Okay, give me ice queen villain
walking down a dark alley
in a haze of fog
surrounded by crows!
--[MANANA] How'd I make you...
--[CHIO] How'd you make me...
[BOTH]
...look so good?
[CHIO] I've never looked
this cool before in my life!
[MANANA yells]
[CHIO]
Let's take some of you now.
Uh, no thanks. I think I'm good.
[chanting] Do it! Do it!
Do it! Do it!
[MANANA]
Have we met?
Like, I'd let her turn
me into cyber trash!
Sorry I value my future!
Not all of us are cam-junkies.
[shutter clicking]
[MANANA]
Hey, boy.
[CHIO] There's a puking cat
photobombing you!
You're trying to be sexy
and the cat's like "Bleh!"
[laughs] This photo
is pure gold!
Oh, the cat's leaving!
Come on, we can try
it again together!
Selfie style!
[MANANA]
Yas!
[CHIO]
Man, that was so much fun!
Sure. How did I end up
getting my picture taken?
Who cares? I made
you look awesome!
But for real. Yours
came out kinda sexy.
Uh, maybe we should
do another shoot
in my room tonight?
Sure. I'll keep this with me
so we can use it again.
[MANANA] You're just gonna
hold it in your hand all day?
[CHIO] No, but it'll
break if I pocket it.
Once we get to school,
I'll find something to wrap
it in and put it in my bag.
[MANANA]
Cool, cool.
[CHIO, MANANA]
Our mission:
smuggle an illegal
substance on campus.
[CHIO, MANANA]
We'll say it's a toy.
Together we guard it
with our lives.
Our school-day mission
is about to begin.
Let this first step be--
Something is stinky.
But I bathed, and wiped,
and used perfume.
[GOTOU] What is that smell?
It's unbearable!
Everyone, stop where you are!
Somebody here has tobacco!
You can lie to your
parents all you want,
but not to my nose!
[CHIO]
Is he part K9 cop?
How can he smell one
used, unlit cigarette?
I'm getting close.
The smell appears
to be growing stronger.
It's you!
No, never mind.
I'm not that bad!
[CHIO]
This is it. This is how it ends.
Was it peer pressure
or temporary insanity?
What was I thinking bringing
a used cigarette to school?
It's not like
I'd play with a bomb
just because it
hadn't exploded yet.
If he finds this thing,
I'm going to be
in some deep doodoo.
I'll get expelled and end up
with a future on the streets.
Oh, shit!
What if he asks to look
through our phones
for some kind of evidence?
Those stupid photos!
It's you.
[CHIO]
I'm dead.
Yeah. I'm so sorry.
And where did you get this?
I saw some lady throw
it out her car window.
So I picked it up off the
ground on my way here, sir.
Oh?
Well, good job, young lady.
I'll go ahead and get
rid of this for you.
Wait, uh...
Chio, don't!
Hey!
I know you're thinking
I'm the one who
smoked it, but I didn't!
[GOTOU]
Hmm? Yeah, I know.
I can tell, because whoever
smoked it was wearing lipstick.
And besides, this is
a pretty strong brand.
No kid could handle it.
And someone like you
wouldn't be smoking.
[CHIO] Um, why wouldn't
"someone like me" be smoking?
You don't know that.
I might be a smoker!
And I do wear lipstick
sometimes! Rude!
I'm bad! You don't know what
kind of secrets I'm hiding.
[MANANA]
Huh?
[GOTOU]
Hmm?
[STUDENTS laughing]
[STUDENT 4B]
Miyamo thinks she's a badass.
[STUDENT 4C] She's supposed
to be intimidating?
All right. Well, that was fun.
Look at these photos.
I have proof. I'm damaged.
Give me the phone!
I'm not gonna pay
for your poor life choices!
[STUDENT 4E]
Chio's School Road .
Kind of early in the day
for that, isn't it?
Oh. One of the first years
picked it up. It's not mine.
Cigarettes are such
a thing of the past.
Only losers and idiots
smoke these days.
[GOTOU]
You think?
I don't know, this brand
is pretty classic.
Many famous authors smoked it
whilst spinning
their literary gold.
[STUDENT 4E]
Really? Wow!
Teachable moment. You should
never prejudge someone
even if they're ruining
their life smoking.
[STUDENT 4E]
Understood!
[STUDENT 4A]
Something's very confusing
about that statement.
[CHIO]
Really? They want a first-year
to determine their career path?
What are you gonna
do with your life?
I dunno. I wrote down that
I wanted to become a teacher.
How come I didn't
know that about you?
It's called strategy, dummy.
If you were a teacher
and knew there was a student
who saw you as a role model,
wouldn't that just
melt your heart?
So, where's the strategy?
Like, what is it
you're trying to get?
Better grades.
You're a scumbag.
[MANANA]
It's all BS.
No one gets a job
unless they're forced to.
Why should I plan for
something I never wanna do?
[CHIO] I don't think
everyone is forced.
There are some jobs
that are actually fun.
[MANANA]
Oh, okay.
Let's make a bet.
[CHIO]
What?
[MANANA]
We'll bet 100 yen.
We go up to the first
adult we see and say,
"Excuse me, is your job fun?"
And if they say they love
their paid slave life,
then you win.
We're really going to walk up
to some rando and ask that?
--Yep!
--[CHIO] It's a trap.
She's got something
up her sleeve, I know it.
[MAN] They can take
this job and shove it!
I just wanna quit.
No. That's cheating!
[MANANA] Hello, sir.
Are you having a bad day?
[CHIO]
She's gonna do it!
Are problems at work
getting you down?
[MAN]
Well, that's not--
Aw. That's not fun, is it?
I wanted a new life.
I figured it's time to grow up.
So I went out and
got myself a job.
And that's when I learned
I fail at everything,
even delivering newspapers!
[CHIO]
Cool bike.
I guess it belongs
to the newspaper guy.
Wait a minute, is that...
Oh, my god, it is!
It's that crazy dude
from the biker gang!
[ANDOU] All of my customers
keep bitchin' about me.
Which means my boss
is gonna rip me a new one.
So what you're trying to say
is your job is no fun, right?
And you hate it?
It's a challenge, but
every job has some, yeah?
At least I'm contributing.
Huh?
It has nothing to do
with not being fun.
It's more of a personal
preference thing.
Others might get off
on tossin' news,
but it's not really my style.
[MANANA]
So now you're too cool for it?
Matter of fact, what am I doin'?
I should just set these
stacks on fire and quit.
[MANANA]
Woo-hoo.
[CHIO]
I object!
You wanna quit on
changing your life
because it's just
not your style?
Is being a loser more your jam?
Wha--? Bloody B--
[CHIO] But you know what?
No more excuses!
We're gonna help you out today!
I mean, we still
have a little time
before we have to get to school,
so my friend and I
are gonna help you
deliver the rest. 'Kay?
Yeah, okay.
I've only got a few
of these bastards left.
Let's do it!
[CHIO]
Come on, Manana!
[MANANA]
Why?
[ANDOU]
First stop is down here!
--[CHIO] But your bike is--
--[ANDOU] Don't need it.
These are my last papers.
You two deliver to the
house with the red roof
--and the one across from it.
--[CHIO] You got it!
I'll get the rest
on the other side.
--Bloody--
--[CHIO] I'm Miyamo
and this is Nonomura.
'Sup, bruh.
Nice to meet you. I'm Andou.
Gee, thanks for making me do
someone else's work
for them, Chio.
Hey, you know what?
You're welcome.
Know why?
Because you just might
discover the joy of working.
It's already really late,
so just ring the doorbell
and hand it to them directly,
and smile.
Why do I have to be
the one to do it?
[doorbell rings]
[WOMAN 4A grumbles]
Oh, hi. Here you go.
Hope you enjoy. Sorry it's late.
I already saw all this on TV!
[laughing]
[MANANA] Happy place.
Cute puppies, dead Chio...
[CHIO]
Cool, so, I'll do the next one!
[doorbell rings]
[WOMAN 4B]
Hmm?
[CHIO]
Hand-delivered just for you!
I'm so sorry it's a little late!
But you know what they say,
better late than--
[groans]
Ow! Stop!
Am I bleeding? Oh, nope.
Nope, I'm good.
[MANANA mumbling] Never getting
a job. Jobs ruin lives.
Must stay away. Must not work.
[gasps]
You handed the papers
to them directly?
Oh, man, I should've warned you.
Delivering a late paper
to anyone from that generation
is conjuring a geriatric wrath.
It's just a newspaper!
I'm not late with
their medication!
[ANDO] They didn't have this
laid-back education system
that exists today.
They studied all night long
just to avoid a beating.
If they can't study
current events
to keep up with conversation,
they revert back to their youths
and become violent!
[CHIO] What? No wonder
they freaked out so hard.
Their whole lives revolve around
thinking they're well-informed.
It's not about the mental
conditioning of 80-year-olds.
It's about you being late, dude!
Why are you so frickin' behind?
I guess I never thought
of it that way.
I keep getting into
these annoying situations
in the morning that set me back.
Damn cops keep comin' up
to me with questions.
I guess I got a little
irritated with them
for interrupting my flow.
[COP] Huh? Your tone
makes me think different.
[ANDOU]
Dude took up half my day.
Here's the thing.
You have resting thug fa--
Hey! I totally get it.
This stuff happens all the
time. It's not your fault!
You mean it?
Little tip from me to you:
you should try to smile more.
You know, let people see
who you really are.
I'm gonna smile, damn it!
[CHIO]
That's the spirit!
[MANANA] What's up with
Chio, the cheerleader?
[MANANA gasps]
[MANANA]
Oh, hell no!
So, where to now?
Just around this corner here.
Hang on.
Damn it. There he is.
[MANANA] The one you
were telling us about?
[CHIO] He's waiting outside?
Is that normal?
[ANDOU]
Yeah, if I'm even a second late,
he stands by his door
waiting for me
while he bitches and
grunts to himself.
If I have to wait
out here any longer,
he's gonna pay my medical bill!
Yeah, and I'm actually several
hours behind today, so...
It's gonna suck rice balls,
but the man needs his news.
Hold on!
When you make the deliveries,
you just have to put them
in the mail slot, right?
--Manana!
--[MANANA] Yeah, yeah, I get it.
[ANDOu]
What are you doing?
Making miracles.
[ANDOU]
Stairs are on the other side!
He's gonna piss himself when
he sees how angry I am now.
Damn kids don't know
the value of a job.
If it's not handed to 'em,
then they don't want it.
Maybe I need to remind this punk
that customers feed his ass
and pay for all his
smart-ass gadgets.
[gasps]
I'm paying for a service
I'm not even getting!
And for that loser to sleep in!
[sneezes]
[MAN 4B]
Where the hell are you?
Spending all my money
on deadbeats.
--Are you okay?
--[CHIO] Shh.
[MAN 4B] What the...?!
When did this get here?
[laughs]
You really are a miracle worker!
[CHIO]
I know, right?
[BOTH laughing]
[CHIO] When you use a dagger,
you don't rely on arm strength.
You brace it with your abs
and use all your
body weight to attack!
[CHIO, MANANA cheering]
[CHIO]
Delivery achievement unlocked!
[CHIO, MANANA] We nailed it
like hammerhead sharks!
[clears throat]
So, uh...
Whoa! You're so close!
Did we miss some?
No, it's not that. I just...
Thank you for, uh...
Well, you... Start over.
What I'm trying to say is,
I'm gonna keep this job,
and it's because of you.
So thanks.
[CHIO]
Good.
I know it's a pain sometimes,
but it can be fun, too, right?
Right.
Okay. Let's go, Chio.
Uh, good meeting you, Andou.
It's been real, I guess.
See ya later?
Hey, Chio, about that guy...
You know it.
Wow. Seriously?
[CHIO]
Yup.
Pay up, beeyatch.
Don't give me that look. I won.
Before we left, he said his
job could be fun at times.
That means I win.
Gimme my money.
[MANANA]
She did not just...
Where my money at?
Gimme dat cash.
[MANANA]
So the uncomfortable flirting...
The unreasonably
caffeinated skipping...
...was all part of her plan
to manipulate some douche-canoe
into saying what she wanted,
so she could make
some extra coin?
Why? Why is she like this?
Now pay up! Come on!
Gimme my money, I earned it!
[MAN 4B]
Chio's School Road !
Miyamo... It's such a pretty
name. She changed my life.
She's an angel sent from above.
[MANANA]
I hate her and her stupid face.
Especially this one.
[CHIO]
Manana's School Road !
You know how you told me
that you became friends
with Hosokawa
by throwing yourself
in the garbage that one time?
What does that even mean?
[CHIO] It means...
that's... what I did?
Jumped in the trash?
Instead of just
looking behind you,
you made her rush
to your rescue?
Everything's a three-act
drama with you, I swear.
Oh? And what would
you have done?
[MANANA] Please. The ambiguous
facial expression!
The what?
Learn from me, Chio.
Make it look like you're
not looking at someone
when you actually are!
How do you look at someone
without looking like
you're looking at them?
[MANANA] First of all,
popular kids hardly ever
notice us plebs, so it's
smart to be cautious.
Second, don't ever wave back.
Just make a noticeable
but vague shift
in your expression.
That way, if they
were waving at you,
it doesn't look like
you ignored them.
If they weren't,
you just keep walkin'!
Either way, no one
else will notice
because you're just
using your face!
Yeah, I get it,
but what does the
expression look like?
--Magic.
--[STUDENT 4F] Morning.
[CHIO] It's one of the popular
girls in Manana's class!
Whoa! Oh, my gosh.
This is exactly what happened
to me the other day!
Is she talking to Manana
or the others behind us?
Moment of truth.
What will she do?
[MANANA]
Hey!
Whoa! That's perfect!
We've got joy, surprise,
and a little hesitation
in the eyes and brows.
Lips may or may not be
on the verge of smiling.
She's doing it.
It looks like she's
not responding,
but she actually is!
Hey, what's wrong?
[CHIO] Holy crap, it works.
It's like a social fly trap!
Are you gonna throw up?
[CHIO]
Or not.
She thinks Manana's either
sick or a giant weirdo.
[MANANA grunts]
I don't know!
My stomach has been killing me.
[screaming]
Do you think maybe
she's possessed?
Whoa, is she having
some kind of fit?
[CHIO]
They're all coming over here!
[STUDENT 4F]
Are you breathing?
Yeah, it happens all
the time, it'll pass soon!
Did you eat?
Should I call an ambulance?
Maybe it's appendicitis!
Oh, that's bad!
You need surgery!
Who's your emergency contact?
[STUDENT 4G]
What if you're dying?
[CHIO]
This sucks.
'Kay, gotta go! Bye!
[CHIO] Next time on
Chio's School Road ,
"Thank You, George,"
and "Mananacchio!"
Lookin' forward to it!
Gimme my money!
[CHIO blabbering]
...is all I got.