[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20A]
The moment it is destroyed,
Golem will begin to sing.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20B]
The tune is one that kills off
artificial cells and causes
wholesale destruction.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20A]
The effects will be felt
in every corner of the universe.
[SOLDIER 25A]
Gatlantean Fleet is in disarray.
Radio is out, too.
[SOLDIER 25B]
They've completely lost control.
Finally.
All ships, move!
Withdraw from the battlefront.
[ZWORDER]
I suspected this.
As a Gatlantean who has eaten
of the Fruit of Knowledge,
I cannot accompany them.
[SANADA]
Kodai, do you read me?
Have the assault team
withdraw quickly.
What now?
This isn't the work
of Golem alone.
Some unknown entity is
destroying the City Empire.
It's absorbing every object
and scrap of energy.
[gasps]
[SANADA]
It can't be.
The Ark of Destruction
is beginning to devour
the City Empire itself.
[SANADA] Lieutenant Keyman,
return to the ship!
At this rate,
the Yamato will be--
[KEYMAN]
XO Sanada.
I have an idea.
[ZWORDER]
The extermination of evil races.
In order to fulfill the duty
given to it by its creators,
the Ark of Destruction
is always evolving,
always seeking the optimal
form for the current moment.
[ZWORDER]
This evolution will continue,
whether the Gatlanteans are
there to witness it or not.
All that is required is a judge
to bring on the destruction.
It needs a human will.
No, wait!
I, Zworder, am human!
Hear me, Ark of Destruction!
It is time for your
true awakening!
[SAITO]
Kodai! You okay?
[ZWORDER laughing]
Please, no!
Stop this, Zworder!
[KODAI]
Don't do it!
[SAITO]
Come on! We need to go!
[KODAI]
No!
[AIHARA] Assault team,
withdraw immediately!
Yamato 's engines have
sustained serious damage!
Engine pressure is
rising, almost critical!
[growls] This hasn't
happened before.
Who knows how long she'll hold?
[SHIMA]
Tokugawa.
Yamato .
[GAMILAN SOLDIER 25A]
Everything is being sucked into
the opening near
the gravity source.
[GAMILAN SOLDIER 25B]
Energy readings at the
City Empire's core
are still rising.
There it is.
The Ark of Destruction.
[SANADA]
Kodai.
[KODAI]
Sanada?
[SANADA] If we want to
put a stop to this,
we have just one chance.
Before the energy
transmutation is finished,
someone must
approach the reactor
and blow it up from the inside.
It's the only way.
From inside.
[KODAI]
Keyman?
[KEYMAN]
Bonds. They drive us all.
On this plane is the last of
the Wave Motion
Excavator Warheads.
[KEYMAN] The Ark is eating
indiscriminately to feed
a thousand years of
unsatiated hunger.
If I act now...
[KODAI]
Wait, Keyman!
It's not just your call!
You turn back!
I'll take your place!
[beeping]
[KODAI]
Please!
I don't want to
lose anyone else!
[KEYMAN grunts]
[KEYMAN groans]
[SAITO]
You're not going alone, Gammy.
I'm coming, too.
I have a request.
Air Corps, escort Captain
Kodai back to the Yamato .
Keep him safe.
There is still so
much he has to do--
Be selfish for once.
[YAMAMOTO]
You're always like this.
Living for others.
Unable to live for yourself.
[YAMAMOTO]
I can't take it anymore.
It's too sad.
[SAITO]
No, it's not.
The way I figure it,
the people who can
only live for themselves are
the ones who're really sad.
Y'know?
Everyone goes through
life hoping to find
something that's truly
precious to them.
[SAITO]
Something irreplaceable.
Something they would
rather die than lose.
[SAITO chuckles]
So, what else can I do?
I've found that precious thing.
So have I!
[NAGAKURA]
Kodai!
Please, let him go.
At the end, please just...
let him be human!
[SAITO]
Kodai!
You'd better do
what my wife says!
[SAITO] Or I'm gonna
have to rough you up!
Saito...
[SAITO yelling]
Gammy!
Move quickly and be
precise, but don't rush!
[KEYMAN]
Akira, you may disagree,
but I've never thought
of my life as a sad one.
[KEYMAN]
I have known the pain of loss,
but only because I had
something to lose.
[KEYMAN]
Still.
[KEYMAN] I am sad that I
cannot hear your voice now.
[KEYMAN] And I am sad that
I cannot see your face now.
[KEYMAN] It's too bad that
for everything gained,
every bit of happiness
experienced,
there always seems to be
an answering sorrow.
Commander, I thank you.
[KEYMAN] That sorrow...
is something I love.
[KODAI]
Yamamoto!
Saito.
Keyman.
--[rumbling]
--[KODAI gasps]
No. But how?
[ZWORDER]
You fools.
It's over.
The destruction
cannot be stopped.
Humanity is finished.
Its future is already lost.
Accept it.
The gift you've been given.
The only salvation that
can end this suffering.
[ZWORDER]
Death.
Farewell, warriors of Earth.
You who will not
pull the trigger.
[OTA] Gatlantis has
begun moving towards
the coordinates of Saturn.
[SANADA] It will take
the remaining chunks
of Saturn's core,
convert them to energy,
and then hit Earth.
[KODAI]
Zworder was right.
It cannot be stopped.
[KODAI]
All hands, abandon ship.
After the Ark's next strike,
Earth may cease to be
a habitable planet.
[KODAI]
But, even so...
As many humans as possible...
...must live on for as
many minutes as they can.
[KODAI] Even if the choices
they must make to do so
are more painful than dying.
[KODAI] Difficult as it is,
people must live on.
[SHIMA gasps]
Kodai.
Kodai stayed behind!
[KODAI]
We must keep fighting
for as long as there is
still a shred of hope.
[KODAI]
I've heard about the G Plan.
I want you to escape
the solar system at once.
You must seek out a new Earth.
Wait, no!
What about you, Captain Kodai?
We can't just--
[KODAI]
Okita.
I'll apologize
on the other side.
[door opens]
[gasps]
[KODAI]
Yuki!
But why?
You shouldn't be here!
If I weren't,
who would navigate?
The Ark.
We'll ram the Yamato in there.
[KODAI gasps]
[YUKI]
Even throwing a near-critical
Wave Motion Engine at it,
we can't sink something
with that mass.
But, before the enemy
finishes replenishing energy,
if we just buy some time,
then more people can escape,
and fewer will die when
it strikes the Earth.
Are you sure?
[YUKI]
It's true.
My memories of you are all gone.
But still. I know you.
And I know that's
what you're thinking.
Yuki.
[YUKI]
Kodai, you can't do this alone.
The Yamato . It's...
They've given us a gift.
Let's speed up the evacuation!
[ZWORDER]
One thousand years ago,
you awakened the
Ark of Destruction.
[ZWORDER] Do you know why
you were able to do that?
[ZWORDER]
Because you are human.
Because you are human,
you curse people and
seek to destroy them.
[ZWORDER]
Because you are human,
you love people and
seek to protect them.
Wave Motion Engine.
Pressure at 200 percent.
The reactor is about
to go critical,
but we should be able to make it
inside the Ark of Destruction.
You feel so warm.
Yuki.
Kodai, I...
[BOTH gasp]
That light, could it be?
Teresa.
[TERESA] Memories are
just an accumulation.
Emotions are what create the
true bonds between people.
[TERESA]
Everything is the work of bonds.
I am only here now because
of my bond with you.
When the Wave Motion
Engine melted down,
it opened a hole leading
into a higher dimension,
bringing out Teresa.
A one-in-a-hundred-million
chance, or was this inevitable?
We humans created a vessel to
bring Teresa into this universe.
The Yamato .
[TERESA] Sometimes, strong
emotions can change a destiny
that has already
been established.
[TERESA] But for such
a reversal to occur,
everything must be in place.
[TERESA]
If any of you had been missing,
I could not have come here.
[TERESA] Like you, I am a
part of the Great Harmony.
Let us go together and discover
the destiny that awaits us.
[KODAI]
I pulled the trigger.
[YUKI]
Kodai, no!
[SAKI]
What a mess.
[SANADA]
Perhaps we are being tested.
[SHIMA]
We've got work to do.
[TERESA] It is all decided
by people's feelings.
If you wish it, the world
you hope for will...