[SHIMA]
Warp complete.
[OTA]
Error correction. 20. 15. 10.
[AIHARA]
Correction data sent.
Transit Wave Motion Gun,
get ready to fire!
[KODAI]
Target scope, open!
All right, targeting comet core.
Open Wave Motion Gun circuit!
[NANBU] Wave Motion
Gun circuit, opening!
Roger. Shutting valves.
[SANADA]
The CRS Booster is connected.
[SAIJO] Neu Desular warping
out at designated point.
Energy charge sufficient.
One hundred twenty percent.
[NANBU]
Ten seconds to fire.
All crew, engage anti-shock
and anti-flare defenses.
[DESLER] My Neu Deusular
will fight for him.
I swear I will protect
the Yamato from
the Transit Wave Motion
Gun's energy radiation.
[KODAI]
Transit Wave Motion Gun,
fire now!
What? How could
this be possible?
It has more power than
the Wave Motion Gun?
What a bizarre bond we share.
Us, and that ship,
guided by Teresa.
Yamato .
[AIHARA] Incoming call
from the Zoelguut !
Yamato crew.
You can rely on Gamilas.
We're exhausting all efforts.
We will send you to the core
of the Comet City Empire.
We hope you'll trust us.
We'll defend the Earth.
Ambassador Burrell.
This has to be a
joint operation.
You'll head straight to
the emperor's throne room
in the Ark of Destruction.
It's not possible via warp.
But with our advanced
technology, it is.
Dimensional Submarine surfacing!
[KODAI gasps]
This is something we
have yet to attempt.
[FLAKEN] Even though
we're using four ships
with specialized equipment,
it's likely that the Yamato
will still have to go in alone.
And there are many risks.
There's no guarantee
of success here.
[HIJIKATA] It's clear.
This, too, is the work of bonds.
The Dimensional Submarine.
Let it take the helm.
All ships, together.
Commence diving at once!
[YABU]
Diving now, sir!
[BERGER] We will hold
steady and fight the enemy
until the Yamato
achieves its goal.
Without fail!
[HEINI] We're almost
to the surfacing point.
[FLAKEN] This is as far as
we can safely escort you.
You're on your own now, Yamato .
I pray we'll meet again.
We're pretty much in
the belly of the beast.
Remain on the lookout
for enemies!
Heat source detected, no ID!
Karakrum-class,
but they're small.
Sizes are all over
the place, in fact.
What is this?
It's just like
Katsuragi's intel told us.
That thing. It's the
Gatlantean mothership.
I think.
All systems, link us to
their automated navigation.
[GOENITZ]
Hm? What is that light?
It's a type of disruption
that utilizes cosmo waves.
We cannot shut it out.
It's a superior code level.
It can only be another
Silver Priestess.
[GOENITZ]
One who possesses the authority
to control this Comet City.
[GOENITZ]
The gate!
It hasn't been opened
in a thousand years!
[ZWORDER]
Sabera!
[gasping]
I see a doll is no
competition for you.
Razera.
Sir!
[ZWORDER]
Show me what you can do.
[AIHARA]
The system jack is successful!
All crew!
This ship will now dive right
into the middle of the enemy!
Space Cavalry, head out!
All planes, take off!
[gasps]
[TOKO grunting]
[TOKO]
No! It isn't taking my commands!
[HIJIKATA]
What happened?
[SANADA]
Damage to our stern, sir!
The rear starboard
side! It's the engine!
Orders, sir?
Go, now!
[shrieks]
Shima, damage report!
The ship can't take much more!
Zworder is aware that
our target is Golem.
He'll defend it at all costs.
[KODAI gasps]
[HIJIKATA]
Have no doubt.
It's kill or be killed.
But, then again,
we've known that all along.
[KODAI]
Break through the front!
[SANADA]
Damage is extensive.
Close all bulkheads now!
[KODAI]
Begin emergency steering!
Cut power to all
non-essential sections!
[KASAHARA] Doctor! There's no
more room in the infirmary!
[DR. SADO]
Put them in the corridor!
You're triaging, right?
[KASAHARA]
Yes, sir!
[DR. SADO]
Keep working! We've got to save
as many as possible!
[YUKI gasps]
[CREW groaning]
[YUKI]
Teresa?
I hope you can hear me.
Teresa.
It's strange.
I don't remember
Terezart at all,
but I feel as if I do, somehow.
[YUKI] So, if you're
out there, tell me.
Is there some deeper
meaning to this suffering?
Something that justifies
all the bloodshed.
Does a reason like
that even exist?
The engine output
still isn't stabilizing.
Navigation doesn't
seem to be affected.
But--
Chief Engineer Tokugawa!
Do you read me?
[YUKI] We are all born alone
and we will die alone, as well.
So why do we even meet
in the first place?
[ANALYZER]
Danger!
[ALL groan]
[DR. SADO gasps]
Analyzer!
Doctor!
Let me go!
Please, he's more
than just a machine.
He's irreplaceable!
[ANALYZER]
Doctor.
Thank you for your kindness.
[YUKI] We've all lost so much,
and we can never get it back.
[CREW screaming]
[YUKI]
Family.
Comrades.
Our most precious memories
of our loved ones.
[YUKI]
I can't bear to lose any more.
[HIJIKATA gasps]
Captain, no!
[YUKI]
Don't take anything else!
[KODAI grunts]
Sir! Captain, stay with me!
Call Doctor Sado!
[HIJIKATA]
No.
[KODAI gasps]
Don't make a fuss.
[HIJIKATA]
Look at those.
Some of them are still under
Toko Katsuragi's control.
Combine them with
the Yamato 's systems
and use them more efficiently.
Make them like an asteroid ring.
Use that to defend
our air forces,
then rush inside the gate
at the first chance.
Can you do that?
Yes!
[HIJIKATA]
Kodai.
The Yamato 's
next captain is you.
[HIJIKATA]
Grasp the future.
[SAIJO crying]
[KODAI sobs]
[KODAI]
The future.
I want everyone to carry out
Captain Hijikata's orders!
[VALSEY gasps]
The magnetron waves.
They seem to be
aligning perfectly
with Toko's cosmo waves.
This is Kodai.
I'm joining up with
the air forces.
From there, we'll go through
the gate as an advance force.
[SAITO]
Roger!
[NAGAKURA]
Enemy spotted ahead.
[KEYMAN]
Hold on. What's that?
[KATO] I've got this guy.
You go on ahead!
[KEYMAN]
He's all yours.
[KATO]
I refuse to run anymore.
Right now I want to live so
bad it might just kill me.
I want to see Makoto's face.
I want to see Tsubasa healthy.
To carry him on my shoulders.
I want to do
everything for them.
All that I couldn't do before.
[KATO]
I will make it back alive.
I swear it!
[KATO]
Just like that, huh?
Pathetic.
I don't care!
I'm not dead yet!
I'll keep fighting
until the very end!
[CROWD murmuring]
Wanna know a secret?
Your daddy is a real-life hero.
It's done. Close the gate.
Engine! Output to maximum!
[KEYMAN]
Kodai! Leave this part to me!
Keyman.
Gate of Lerte. Open.
[TOKO]
I will lead you to Golem.
I can't believe they
made it this far.
[ZWORDER]
Sabera.
I know you can hear me.
[ZWORDER]
Don't shut me out!
Why do you insist on denying me?
[gasps]
[ZWORDER]
You, who know better than anyone
how useless Earthlings are.
And you, the very same one who
opened the Ark of Destruction!
Why?!
Because I never should
have awakened it!
[ZWORDER]
Is that so?
After Mil, our own child,
was murdered twice,
you still choose this?
[TOKO]
Yes.
Your heart is full of sadness
and aching with despair
because of what happened.
[ZWORDER]
A heart.
[TOKO]
You are human!
[TOKO] You were always
more human than anyone!
[ZWORDER]
There you are!
[TOKO gasps]
[KURATA]
Hurry! The door's closing!
[SAITO]
Damn it!
[KURATA groans]
[ZWORDER]
You're quite impressive.
I must admit,
you've done incredibly well
to come this far.
But what will you do now?
See. That woman isn't
protecting you anymore.
[gasps] Toko.
Why?
How could you do that to your--
[ZWORDER]
You dare ask me why?
You, who used her as
you piled up sacrifices
in your desperation to get here.
The very same man who
claimed he would not
pull the trigger?
[ZWORDER] Earthlings,
this is as far as you go.
[YAMAMOTO]
Kodai.
[KODAI]
Right.
--[gun clicks]
--[YAMAMOTO groans]
[YAMAMOTO]
Commander!
[SAITO]
Sorry! I'm a little late!
Take control of Golem, hurry up!
Majesty. We must leave
before it's too late.
"The battle has been decided."
Is that what you're
trying to tell me?
[KODAI]
If you people are truly human,
then there should be
room for dialogue.
What's that?
"Human"?
[KODAI]
Your hope for the future?
He told me the truth.
Sadly, that future...
[ZWORDER]
...is dead now.
[NAGAKURA] How can there
still be so many of them?
[SAITO]
Look out!
Are you... all right?
Now I realize.
[KODAI]
Zworder...
[ZWORDER]
We are human.
It's the truth.
[KODAI]
No, don't!
[SABERA screaming]
[SANADA]
This can't be.
It's devouring the
City Empire itself.
[BURRELL] There it is,
the Ark of Destruction.
[AIHARA] Yamato 's engines
have sustained critical damage!
[YUKI]
We'll ram the Yamato in there.
[KODAI] I don't want
to lose anyone else!
[SAITO]
Kodai!
[KEYMAN]
Grasp the future.