[SANADA]
Do you remember the first time
Captain Okita collapsed and I
was forced to take command?
[KODAI]
Yes.
[SANADA] In that moment,
when every second counted,
I was so focused
on acting rationally
that I let eight
crewmembers die.
[KODAI]
XO...
[SANADA] Rational thought is
by far our greatest weapon.
But even it has its limits,
wouldn't you agree?
[KODAI]
That's, uh...
[SANADA]
Like Captain Okita showed
with his swift decisiveness,
in the heat of battle
a commander needs the ability
to think in a way that
transcends rationality.
Tactical Commander Kodai,
as of now,
I am giving you full command
of the Yamato on this voyage.
[gasps]
I want you to serve
as Acting Captain.
You're the best man for
the job. You've proven that.
It's time.
Our strike team will soon
have the dock surrounded.
In the worst-case scenario,
if they have mutinous intent
and lock themselves
inside the Yamato
we'll keep them pinned down.
[LEADER 4A] At location. Unable
to confirm visual on Yamato.
[SERIZAWA] What?! But it
shows here on our screen.
I'm looking right at it!
They must have tampered
with the cameras.
They blinded us!
What about secondary sensors?
They didn't just vanish
into thin air, find them!
[SOLDIER 4A]
No heat signature,
and no sign of the
ship leaving port.
They've gone under.
What was that, sir?
The old underground city--the
dock is still connected to it.
Get me a visual on
the lower levels, now!
[UNCF OPERATOR 1C]
Patching in cam data, on screen.
[SERIZAWA growls]
They're making fools of us.
Those bastards.
Mind your temper, Admiral.
These are still the heroes
who saved the Earth.
Captain Okita.
I have no doubts about making
this voyage, but even so,
I'm scared...
Scared of myself...
That I might be the one
who gives the order
to use the Wave Motion Gun.
If I wanted to, I could cut
the circuit now and seal it off.
If I truly object to
Earth's military policies,
that's the right thing to do.
But still, if any of
the crew were to die
as a result of not having it,
well what then?
How do I make that choice?
[OKITA]
Kodai...
[KODAI gasps]
Show your resolve.
[KODAI]
Captain!
[UNCF OPERATOR 4A]
Ship sighted off the coast,
approaching dome from the
southwest. It's the Kirishima !
What?! That ship?
We retired it.
Who's operating it?
They're really doing it.
[KODAI]
We should go!
No matter who it is,
or how far away they are!
Was this the only way, Kodai?
There'll be no turning back.
Not from this.
This way! Get to the lifts!
They've descended into the
abandoned underground city.
Send another unit
around to the coast.
They can't hide
down there forever.
Search every nook and cranny!
Serizawa.
Stand down until they've
all boarded the Yamato.
Then, I will address them.
[SERIZAWA]
But--!
You are not to attack them.
We'll end this peacefully.
Understood, sir. But we should
prepare for all contingencies.
If they choose to
disobey a direct order
and attempt to launch...
...we need to be ready
to keep them in check.
Oh, ho! They're all here!
--[KAMO] Yamazaki!
--[YOSHIDA] Yamazaki!
[YAMAZAKI]
Kamo! Yoshida! Better hurry.
The old man's waiting on you.
[YOSHIDA, KAMO]
Sir!
[TOKUGAWA] There's not enough
time for a full tune-up.
She may not be in
great shape right now,
but we'll definitely make
the Yamato fly again.
[YOSHIDA, KAMO]
Sir!
[NANBU]
The defense satellite.
On its current trajectory,
we'll be within its firing range
by the time we launch.
You really think they'll use it?
[SANADA] It's possible.
This is a rebel ship, after all.
[TOKUGAWA]
The old girl's warming up,
but I recommend we try
not to push her too hard
right out of the gate.
What do you say, Ota,
you up for manning the helm?
Me?!
If he were coming, it's safe
to say he'd be here by now.
[OTA]
So... Shima said no?
Well, mutiny and treason
aren't for everyone, I guess.
What's our status?
Oh, uh, well...
Command is already dispatching
the defense satellite.
[AIHARA] Message from
Command Headquarters.
They're ordering us
to open a channel.
Put it through. On main panel.
This is Commander-in-Chief
of the Earth Defense Force
Heikuro Todo, speaking.
To the honorable crew
of the Yamato ,
who have served the Earth like
none other in human history,
please listen.
We were saved from
the brink of extinction
thanks to the generous...
Broadcast this
for the whole ship.
Right. Aye-Aye, sir.
[TODO] ... to repay that debt
by answering the call
of others in need.
I understand those feelings.
However, I want you to think.
We have just received
an unknown transmission
of uncertain origin and intent.
Until the facts can
be fully understood,
it is important not
to act too hastily.
The Yamato is a powerful weapon.
If she intervenes unduly in an
unknown star system's conflicts,
that could lead to
unforeseen consequences
that place Earth
in danger, as well.
I do not believe that is a
future any of us wish to see.
It's not too late.
For the good of us all,
leave the Yamato and
surrender peacefully.
It's hard. But please...
Find the courage to do so.
Acting Captain Susumu Kodai
speaking. Message acknowledged.
We'll give you
five more minutes.
Everyone, I want you
to listen closely.
This is the reality we face.
What the commander
says is correct,
but the Yamato will
set sail on schedule.
So long as someone is
seeking help, we must go,
no matter who it is.
Not out of duty, but
because we wish to show
the people of Earth that
this is who we can be.
Anyone with doubts
should disembark now.
Stay or go. You are
all free to choose.
[TOKUGAWA]
Come on, Acting Captain,
there's no need
to be so serious.
Everyone here knows the score.
This isn't their first voyage,
they knew what they
were signing up for.
[YAMAZAKI] This is the engine
room. No crew disembarking.
[KITANO] Tactical Division.
No one is leaving.
Y'see? Told ya.
[HIRATA] Accounting Division.
We're all staying.
[MISAKI] Operations Division.
We're in, too.
[KIRYU]
Technology Division.
Confirming our
intentions to stay.
Navigation Division...
Navigation Division
reporting for duty!
Let's set sail!
Ota. I'll take the helm for now.
[OTA] Heh. Just be
gentle with her, okay?
They took out
the Control Room!
[OTA] Dockyard Control System
access has been cut off!
They're making sure
we can't flood the dock.
[KODAI] Close all lower hatches.
Don't let them in.
So what's our next
move, Captain?
[AIHARA]
Call from Engineer Yamazaki.
Put it on the main panel.
The dock's main system
is completely offline.
Not only can we not flood
the dock, we have no way
to disengage the gate
or gantry locks.
But, if the Sub-Control
Room is still intact,
we should be able to
activate the flood control
and lock systems from there,
and patch them back
in to the Yamato.
But, that means--
Someone will have to
risk going out there
to manually reboot the system
and initiate the transfer.
That's right.
It's not ideal, but it
may be our only option.
Take Hoshina and Kiryu.
You three, go make it happen.
We'll be counting on you
to get those doors open.
Sir!
Nanbu, bring the guns online.
Give them some covering fire.
[NANBU]
Aye-aye.
[KODAI]
No casualties, understood?
[NANBU]
I know, I know.
[SOLDIER 4B]
Their guns are live! Fall back!
[KODAI] Be sure not to
breach the dock walls.
[NANBU]
Output's at minimum.
[SOLDIER 4C]
They've opened fire!
[SOLDIER 4D]
Go! Go!
Be careful.
We've got this.
Let's move.
[SOLDIER 4E] Up top!
Three crew members on foot!
[SOLDIER LEADER 4A]
Go! Take them into custody!
[CREW panting]
Just through there!
Uh!
[SOLDIER 4F grunting]
[YAMAZAKI]
Hurry, go!
[SOLDIER 4F groans]
[SOLDIER 4G] Targets no longer
attempting to escape.
We are currently engaged!
[gasps] Hoshina!
No Misaki, wait!
It's booting up.
Stand by to transfer
control to the Yamato.
[SOLDIER LEADER 4A]
Withdraw!
[HOSHINA] This is Hoshina
in the Sub-Control Room.
We've successfully opened
the flood valves.
[KIRYU] Now transferring
system controls to the Yamato.
[OTA]
Here it comes!
Transmission of system
control program confirmed.
[SOLDIER 4E]
They're locking us out!
Activate sub-engine.
[SOLDIER LEADER 4A] Yamato
is preparing for departure.
All men evacuate!
Water level, clearing
broadside observation rooms.
[KODAI]
Hold all hatches.
Don't close them until
everyone's back on board.
We have to hurry!
If the water rises much higher,
we'll be cut off from the ship.
Stay back! We've still got a few
of them dug in down there.
We don't have time for this!
Hoshina!
[HOSHINA] The water's already
come in this far?
[KIRYU]
We have to get off this floor.
[SOLDIER 4H] Water's risin'
fast. Gettin' dicey in here.
What do we do now?
I don't know, but I hate
that the only thing keeping
the Yamato from leaving is us.
[MISAKI]
Hoshina!
[gasps]
Hoshina! This way!
[ENOMOTO] Saijo, you okay?
It's dangerous here.
We have to get inside.
But Yamazaki and the others!
C'mon. We've held this
one as long as we can.
There's still the upper
hatch, they'll make it.
Kiryu! Hoshina! Yamazaki!
[OTA] Water level has
surpassed rear hatch limit.
Closing bulkheads to
prevent further flooding.
[SANADA]
Send a collection team
and have them standing
at the ready.
[HOSHINA] Bridge, raise
the water intake rate.
We four--Kiryu, Misaki,
Yamazaki, and Hoshina--
will see the Yamato
off from here.
But, why...? There's time!
Even without us there, we
know the crew of the Yamato
is more than capable of making
this voyage a success,
and we'll be awaiting
your safe return.
We take great pride knowing we
played a part in helping you
begin this journey.
Wherever you go
our hearts will go with you.
[KODAI]
Yamazaki...
You have all of our thanks.
[OTA] Water level
is clearing the bridge.
Dock flooding is complete.
Gantry locks... release.
[KODAI] All crew, remain
at battle stations,
ready to depart.
Dead slow ahead, 0.5.
[TOKUGAWA]
Gate locks, release.
Yamato, passing through
departure channel.
[SOLDIER 4G] The Yamato
has entered ocean waters.
[SERIZAWA growls] Clearly,
they've left us with no choice.
Defense satellite,
prepare to fire!
[TOKUGAWA] Injecting energy
into the Wave Motion Engine.
Sub-engine, increase from
second speed to third speed.
Ramp up for 30 seconds
to one s-knot.
W-Was that?
Wave Motion Engine,
now releasing shut-off
valve to the cylinder.
Five minutes until wave
motion engine ignition.
[KODAI] Shima, sure wish
we had you for this part.
[TOKUGAWA] Wave Motion Engine
internal pressure is rising.
Energy charge at 90%
and climbing steadily.
Prepare to ignite
the main engine
and ascend as soon
as we reach sea level.
[KODAI] Sub-engine, maximum
speed... 40-degree ascent.
Two minutes until sea level.
[TOKUGAWA] Internal engine
pressure levels near maximum.
Energy charge is now... 100%.
[TOKUGAWA] Two minutes to
Wave Motion Engine ignition.
[SHIMA]
Thanks for filling in, Kodai.
[KODAI]
Shima!
Sorry I'm late.
You made it!
We'll talk later, all right?
Flywheel activation
in ten seconds.
One minute until
we reach sea level.
Sub-engine currently
at maximum output.
Wave Motion Engine
internal pressure
has now reached 120%.
Activate flywheel.
Activating flywheel.
Main engine ignition...
ten seconds.
[SHIMA]
5...
...4...
..3... 2... 1.
Engaging flywheel... Ignite!
Yamato, to the sky!
[SHIMA] We've left the water.
Angle of ascent: 20 degrees.
Atmospheric flight mode.
Deploying wings.
[SAIJO] Thermonuclear reactions
detected at one o'clock.
Range: 5,000 kilometers.
Elevation: 27.
Nanbu. Guns one and two.
Prepare to fire.
Seven targets. Inputting orbits.
Main guns one and two ready.
Fire!
[TODO]
Okita's children have left us.
That's does it. This time
they've crossed the line.
For the honor of the
Earth Defense Force,
I'll stop the Yamato.
[SERIZAWA] We will secure the
Yamato. No matter the Outcome.
[KODAI]
Quick! Crew to battle stations!
[SHIMA]
Come on! A little longer!
[TOKUGAWA]
Release asteroids!
[SANADA] Depth charge
launchers standing by!
[SAIJO] Ten seconds until
contact with the Andromeda.