[alarms blaring]
Deploy the main wings!
Main wing power is cut!
They can't deploy!
[YUKI]
Eight thousand to Gatlantis!
[HIJIKATA]
Chief Engineer!
No response from the engine!
[AIHARA] Emergency call
from the Antares .
"We are standing by
behind the Yamato .
We must withdraw soon,
or it will be too late.
We cannot stay much longer.
Use all means to escape, ASAP."
[HIJIKATA sighs]
[HIJIKATA]
Okita, Forgive me.
Attention, Yamato crew.
All hands, abandon ship!
[HIJIKATA] Our engine is
damaged, and we are being
pulled into the enemy's
gravitational field.
In all sections, crew will
proceed to evacuation stations.
I repeat: abandon ship.
Transfer to the
Antares behind us.
I won't.
Shima.
I'll stay! I'll stay
on the Yamato !
That was an order!
[TOKUGAWA]
Shima.
I promise you, we all
feel the same way.
Captain Hijikata, too.
[TOKUGAWA] But if we don't move,
the crew will hesitate.
We need to set an example
for them to follow.
Let's go.
It hurts, but we have a duty
to those under our command.
Tokugawa.
[ANALYZER] Limit for successful
withdrawal is approaching.
Time remaining to escape.
Approximately 600.
XO Sanada, head starboard!
Kodai, you get to the port side,
help evacuate the crew.
[KODAI, SANADA]
Roger!
[HIJIKATA] Chief Engineer
Tokugawa, in accordance
with regulations, lock
the Wave Motion Engine.
Sir.
[HIJIKATA] The Cosmo Tigers
and all shipborne planes
are to disembark
immediately with as many
crew members aboard
as you can carry.
Head for the Antares !
All hands, evacuate
now. Don't hesitate!
Your duty is to survive and
carry on the Yamato 's legacy.
The battle has only just begun!
Live, and support the Earth's
future in your own way!
Kato!
Lieutenant Keyman!
It's hopeless. No
matter what you do.
[YUKI]
That's not true! Quick, get up!
We need to go!
Give me a hand. She won't move!
[rattling]
[yelps]
[HIJIKATA]
Hurry.
[ANALYZER] Auxiliary power
is below ten percent.
Decreasing gravity
inside the ship.
[CREW yelling]
[gasps]
[KISHIDA]
XO Sanada!
[ANALYZER] Limit for
withdrawal is imminent.
Navigation with the thrust
of a shipborne plane
will be impossible.
[HIJIKATA]
Antares . This is Yamato .
We are cutting off the
evacuation of crew now.
The Antares is to reverse
course and withdraw at once.
Good luck.
[ANDROMEDA XO] All shipborne
planes from the Yamato
have been taken in.
Antares is withdrawing.
[ANDROMEDA XO] Yamato is
falling to the Comet Empire.
Communications have cut off.
Yamato . I promise you.
[CREW 19A] Higher-dimensional
energy readings
coming from the Comet Empire!
They're missiles!
Turn 180 degrees!
Withdraw at once!
No. Is this...?
Is that a massive
Wave Motion Shield?
It can't be.
[SAKI] That's far enough,
Gatlantis! You shall not pass!
[GOENITZ] Under the order of the
all-powerful Emperor Zworder,
I address all rulers
of planet Earth.
[GOENITZ]
I have received your response,
and I accept your position.
[GOENITZ] I respect your will
to fight to the very end,
until your last soldier falls.
I will face you with honor.
Before it comes to that.
Please allow me to present
your kind with a gift.
I have heard that, as a result
of the prior war with Gamilas,
scores of innocent
children on your planet
suffer in agony from a
heretofore incurable disease.
[GOENITZ]
I will send the data necessary
to create a treatment for them.
Once you have it, you will
be able to save lives
that would have
been lost before.
In recognition and
gratitude for a certain
soldier's love for his son,
I humbly offer this cure to you.
[KURATA]
I can't believe it.
The captain couldn't escape.
Nagakura, either.
What about Kodai
and Officer Mori?
Even the Gammy.
[KATO gasps]
[screams]
[KURATA]
What are you doing?
I just wanna die!
Please, just let me die!
[SANADA] He says he'll
accept any punishment.
Those are Lieutenant
Kato's exact words.
--Please, sir--
--[SERIZAWA] Do you think
this is a joke? We cannot
ever make this public.
That a former hero
sold out his own ship
to save his son's life!
This fact is to be
kept classified!
If he insists on
seeking atonement,
let him fight and die in battle.
[GROUP gasps]
Welcome. Are you all right, sir?
[SANADA] Yes, I'm fine. The
Yamato , on the other hand...
[NIIMI gasps]
[SHIMA]
It's similar.
[AIHARA] You can tell
it's a Yamato -class ship.
[GINGA AI] Course to combat
calculations complete.
Route decided.
XO Kanzaki, Command AI
has determined our course.
[KANZAKI]
Accepted. Share it.
Do you do everything that way?
Yes, mostly.
The Ginga was meant to
be run by autonomous AI.
A next-generation ship,
ahead of her time.
[YAMAZAKI] The future looks
more and more extreme.
It's the most efficient
way. That's all.
[NANBU]
Approving the decisions of AI?
Is that the only work
humans do here?
[SAKI]
I'm sure it will be, eventually.
I welcome you aboard.
This is Spaceship Ginga .
And I'm her captain, Saki Todo.
Now, Please follow me
to Central Operations.
[SAKI] As you're all aware,
one of the Gamilan wall's
functions also interferes
with its warp processes.
Preventing Gatlantis from
making a dimension jump.
Our objective is
simply to defend
the Gamilan wall,
first and foremost.
The problem will come once
the second wave hits.
[SAKI] Many of those ships
carry antimatter missiles.
If the wall is broken,
Earth will be in
immediate danger.
And so, that's why I
have proposed an ambush
by a small, elite force.
Using the Ginga 's
shields, we can cut
to the front of the
enemy's reinforcement fleet
and crush them before
they reach their target,
which is the main fleet.
We are all in
pursuit of perfection.
In the time fault,
a next-generation AI
keeps simulating its own growth.
And the data is
continually being
updated here on the Ginga .
In any case, it will
take time before the AI
can surpass humans,
but that time is coming.
To that end, we would
like the accumulated
skillsets of the Yamato
crew to also be fed
into the Ginga 's AI system.
You mean you wanna copy
all of our knowledge?
We will be splitting your
group between the first
and second bridges very shortly.
From that point forward,
your commands will be traced.
Of course, we have
clearance from HQ for this.
The G Plan's success depends
on it, and HQ agrees.
[SANADA]
The G Plan.
[SAKI] The Yamato sank
in order to ensure
the survival of humans on Earth.
So, we must transfer the DNA
of the Yamato to this ship.
[GINGA AI]
Proposing activation of CRS.
[SAKI] Accepted. Ginga !
Full speed ahead!
[KANZAKI] The enemy fleet--
it's on the move.
Set the rate of CRS
operation to 80 percent.
[GINGA AI]
Injecting Wave Motion Energy.
Beginning amplification.
[NIIMI] Confirming resonance
from Wave Motion Cores to fleet.
Wave Motion Shield output
has reached 750,000 TPA.
And it's still rising.
Who knew the Cosmo
reverse System
had power like this?
Well, of course.
This ship inherited its
heart from the Yamato .
Even without the ability
to resuscitate a planet,
you won't find a better
Wave Motion Energy
control device anywhere
else out there.
But we're not equipped
with a Wave Motion Gun,
are we?
No, The Cosmo
Reverse rejects it.
Not just the Wave Motion Gun.
Even when we try to use
conventional armaments,
the system just malfunctions.
The cause is unclear.
That's why we can't do any
fighting, even in defense.
We must rely on
the escort fleet.
[SANADA] That's how it was
meant to be. I should know.
I designed the Ginga to be
solely an exploration vessel.
And, to think, it would
be used like this.
[KANZAKI] Wave Motion Shield
attrition rate 8,000!
We should move up.
The escort fleet needs
to be within firing range.
[GINGA AI]
With our current strength,
effective bombardment
is impossible.
Proposing the implementation
of Project Black Bird.
Accepted.
[SANADA]
Black Bird.
Unmanned shipborne
planes, already?
[KANZAKI] Each of the
Black Bird crafts carries
a mass-produced
Wave Motion Core.
These will be scattered
throughout the enemy fleet.
Then amplified by our Cosmo
Reverse to cause a meltdown.
[SANADA]
The interference waves produced
by the Wave Motion
Resonance will render
the enemy fleet inoperable.
This technique--
the Yamato used it
at the 11th planet.
That's correct.
But no matter how
cutting edge their AI,
it can't reach the enemy's
center in this situation.
[SANADA gasps]
Right. Which is why
someone volunteered.
A capable pilot will lead
them straight to the center.
That pilot. Is it Kato?
But that's suicide!
If he leaves the warp
interference area,
he'll be exposed to
attacks from every angle!
Deploy all existing resources.
We'll delay the enemy's
advance ten days.
In that time, 100 days will
pass within the time fault.
That means dozens of new
Wave Motion Gun ships
will be completed.
Those will be
deployed to the front
and buy us another ten days.
Then ten more.
And more.
If we can continue
this, no matter
how great the enemy's numbers --
[SHIMA]
What about the people?
With respect, there won't
be enough to man the ships.
We're one step away
from an unmanned fleet.
The Ginga and Black Birds
are proof of that.
[screaming]
[SAKI] With the data collected
from Gatlantean prisoners,
production of artificial
soldiers is drawing closer.
[SAKI]
One hundred days.
If we can just hold
out for 100 days...
We're losing Wave Motion
Cores to targeted fire!
[GINGA AI]
Emergency proposal:
begin resonance at once.
[SANADA, NIIMI gasp]
Have all the Black Birds
pull back right away!
Black Bird team,
withdraw immediately!
Kato, no!
[GINGA AI]
Begin resonance.
[SAKI] Accepted.
Inject Wave Motion Energy!
[SHIMA]
This is insanity.
Sanity has never won any wars.
Eliminate that which
is not needed and employ
any means that might
give us advantage.
Secure victory as
efficiently as possible.
I see. That's the G plan, is it?
Not quite, the G plan is--
Are you sure about this
strategy, Captain Todo?
[NIIMI]
When I think about your mother,
I can understand how you feel.
But, then, when I think
of the real you--
[SAKI]
That's enough.
My mother and father
are irrelevant.
Sentimentality is
useless, Kaoru.
[SAKI] Those without power
are destined to perish.
We carved that truth
into our very bones
in the war with Gamilas.
So, no matter what
it might cost me,
I will live.
[KATO] Why? Why do you
refuse to let me die?
[NAGAKURA]
What's up?
I just got this weird feeling,
like someone was crying.
Probably just the wind.
[SAITO]
Yeah.
[KEYMAN] Keyman here.
The fog's getting thicker.
See anything from up there?
[YAMAMOTO]
No, nothing.
[KEYMAN]
We'll drive around a bit longer.
You can return to the ship.
It's dangerous to be
flying in this fog.
[YAMAMOTO]
Roger.
Where is this? It's weird.
[NAGAKURA] We should be
in the White Comet, right?
This planet seems uninhabited.
I can't imagine Gatlantis
having a base here.
Do you think it
might be possible
that we were sent to a
planet tens of thousands
of light years away?
[KEYMAN]
We shouldn't speculate too much
without more information.
It could warp the way
we look at things.
How 'bout a warning?
Of all places, why there?
[ZWORDER] Is this the
guidance of Teresa, as well?
[GAIREN] That planet is
still very much alive.
If it reacts to the blood
of a Zemurian, then...
[ZWORDER]
I am well aware.
She's already met her fate.
[YUKI]
Hello? And who are you?
[ZWORDER]
Huh?
What's this? How ironic.
Yuki!
Yuki.
I'm so glad.
You finally woke up.
You should probably
rest a bit longer.
I'll go let Doctor Sado
know you're awake.
Who's that?
[gasps]
Who are you?
Sorry.
[NAGAKURA]
She lost all her memories
from the last four years?
--[KODAI] Why?
--[GAIREN] Do you truly intend
to disrupt the
slumber of the dead?
[YAMANAMI] I swear.
I will save the Yamato .
[ZWORDER]
Let us end the suffering.