You can't mean that
Gatlanteans are like humans!
Navigator Ichinose!
Yes, according to data from
the battle near Saturn.
They're human weapons
that don't hesitate
to perform suicide bomb attacks.
As far as The White Comet,
it's a weapon of mass
destruction left
by the Aquarians.
And the Gatlanteans
are using it to--
[ICHINOSE] But, still,
they have human forms!
If they were
artificial life forms,
then they might be able
to mechanize themselves
much more efficiently and
do a lot more damage.
[VILHO]
Inferno Cannon.
All ships have completed
the energy charge.
Heh. End them.
Curses.
[VILHO] High energy readings
coming from beneath the ring!
[gasps]
[VALSEY]
This is simply impossible!
That planet was very
nearly destroyed
in the war with Gamilas.
They should not possess
this level of firepower.
This is quite ugly, Valsey.
It is unacceptable for the fleet
you were given by the emperor
to retreat or alter its course!
If you are a true Gatlantean,
you will fight and die.
Sir.
[SADO]
Whoa! This is unbelievable!
Where could you have found--
[KATO] So that means you
think it's real? Doctor.
Can this pill treat
Planetary Bomb Syndrome?
Yes. At least I think so.
But this is a simple clinical
trial using artificial cells.
[gasps]
[KATO]
I see.
He can get better.
He will get better.
Can this sample be
mass produced?
Well, now. That's an entirely
different matter altogether.
When it comes to actually
producing the medication,
I don't know.
[gasping]
[SADO] But before we get to
that, how did you acquire this?
[KATO gasps, panting]
[SADO]
Hey! Come back!
[door creaks]
I take it you understand.
If you give him that drug,
your child will surely survive.
As will all the other children
who suffer from that illness.
[KATO gasping]
The formula is simple. I was
able to make it right here.
It's just a matter of--
[KATO grunts]
Who is it?
Tell me who it is you're
working with! Talk!
[chuckles] Go ahead,
kill me if you want.
If I die, so will he.
Is that what you want?
Tell me why.
Why are you doing this?
[TOKO gasping]
[KATO]
With all the power you have,
your people could easily
destroy the Yamato and Earth.
So, why?
[TOKO]
It's a game.
[gasps]
A game where the rules are
that love makes people suffer.
So, have no doubt that I
will be true to my word.
Otherwise, the game wouldn't
be any fun, would it?
[GAIREN]
It all makes sense.
Now I understand.
That's how they've
achieved this.
[ZWORDER]
They use a time fault.
Sabera!
[SABERA]
Imperial Star Gatlantis.
Phase transition dimension jump!
Now back down, Valsey.
Yes, sir.
[COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER 17A]
The White Comet has appeared!
Projected course is Earth!
Attention, fleets! Withdraw,
but remain ready to fire.
Keep aim!
We will now commence Plan M.
Tsubasa...
[YAMANAMI] According to
reports from the Yamato,
the White Comet's core
is believed to be
an artificial fortress
the size of a planet.
All fleets, assume
multi-formation!
We will show them
what we're made of!
We will pinpoint the base, and
with simultaneous bombardment
we will destroy it!
[BURRELL] Don't you think
this is being a bit hasty?
We have yet to fully identify
the actual nature of the comet.
[PRESIDENT] All due respect,
this is Earth's problem,
and we must solve it.
To prepare for
coming negotiations,
our best option is to
strike the comet itself.
I see.
Is that truly your view,
Mister President?
Yes, of course.
Deploy gravity
spread and prepare.
Fire!
[YAMANAMI] All ships, prepare
to fire Wave Motion Guns.
[beeping]
[COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER 17A]
Comet is accelerating further.
[ANDROMEDA XO]
Gravity field convergence rate
has reached expected value.
All guns,
target the comet's core.
Set 20 and 45.
[ANDROMEDA XO]
Setting 20, 45!
Shift Wave Motion Gun from
Dispersion to Convergence.
All ships move together.
Energy charge, 120%!
[YAMANAMI] Engage anti-shock
and anti-flare defenses.
[ANDROMEDA XO]
Prepare to fire in... 10...
...9...
...8...
...7...
...6... 5...
...4... 3...
...2...
...1!
[YAMANAMI]
Fire!
[gasps]
Did we succeed?
Now we shall crush them.
All ships, charge energy
to Wave Motion Guns.
Wave Motion Guns... Fire!
[COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER 17A]
Gravity gradient rising!
Measurement impossible!
Turn around!
All ships, withdraw!
[COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER 17A]
The Wave Motion Gun Muzzle!
[ANDROMEDA XO]
It's been destroyed!
The Comet! It's pulling us in!
Engine output dropping!
[YAMANAMI grunts]
[COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER 17A]
Collision with Apollo Norm!
What's that?
[YASUDA]
Commander Yamanami.
Save yourselves.
The Apollo Norm
can't hold any longer.
Captain Yasuda.
[YASUDA] We will push
the Andromeda out with our
remaining power. Yamanami,
you made a valiant effort.
[YAMANAMI]
Yasuda...
Good luck to you.
[laughing]
[NANBU]
Wha... What is that thing?
[YUKI]
I think it's Gatlantis's...
[OTA] How are we
supposed to fight it?
[HIJIKATA]
Kodai.
We're betting on the Transit
Wave Motion Gun.
Sir.
[HIJIKATA] From person to
person, the power of bonds
which works across
the vast universe,
will defeat the Comet Empire.
Or so Teresa said.
So, now, let us
believe her words.
Bonds brought us
aboard this ship,
and into this decisive battle.
And the only thing that can
turn that bond into power
is each of our individual wills.
[PRESIDENT]
We humans of Earth are proud.
We have no intention of bending
the knee to these invaders.
Do not forget
we crawled back up
from the precipice of utter
ruin three years ago.
[PRESIDENT] We humans of
Earth will never give in.
We will fight, united,
to the very last.
[PRESIDENT] For the ideals
of freedom and peace.
And for the future
of our children!
[TOKO laughs]
[gasps]
[TOKO] The only thing that
can save a dying child
is a parent's pure love.
Isn't that true?
It is a love that
cannot be replaced.
It is so pure and
yet so... selfish.
Powerful enough to destroy
everything, too.
Woman! What have you done?
Tsubasa...
[HARADA]
The day Tsubasa was born--
for the first time,
I think I finally understood
my purpose in life.
Suddenly everything
took on new meaning.
This world we live in is truly
full of horrible suffering.
But still, this innocent
child was born into it.
It doesn't even matter
why it happened.
He's here now, and because
of that, I'm happy.
Happy I met you,
and that we had this child.
[KATO cries]
[HARADA]
We don't need anything else.
We can be happy just as we are.
[KATO]
I'm sorry...
...Tsubasa...
Daddy's going to hell.
[KODAI]
What now?
[SHIMA]
Chief Engineer, our propulsion!
Wave Motion Engine has stopped!
It can't be. The Anti-Wave
Motion Lattice is--?
[KODAI gasping]
[alarm blares]
[OTA] We're entering the Comet
Empire's Gravity Field!
[SAKI]
I will not allow you to pass!
Gatlantis!