[panting]
[ZURVIVAL yells]
[NOLL grunting]
[BOTH grunting]
[NOLL groans]
[ZURVIVAL yells]
[ZURVIVAL pants, yells]
[JUDGE 10A]
Enough!
You show much improvement,
Sir Noll. You fought well.
[NOLL gasping]
[GORLAND] I'm sure it's
clear from your match
that Noll is still
lacking something.
I'd like to help him gain it.
He'll soon be facing
his first real battle,
he needs to be sharp.
So you're taking him
Sand Dragon hunting?
That's right.
We'll go with a small party,
so it shouldn't affect
Terezart's defenses.
[ZURVIVAL laughs]
[ZURVIVAL]
I'd actually welcome not having
the mighty Gorland Fleet
hovering over my head
for a while.
With you here, our Zurvival
Land Combat Division
might as well be on leave.
Have your hunt!
Take the entire fleet
with you if you like.
Our division can guard this
measly planet with men to spare.
[GORLAND chuckles]
Of course. You never change.
Neither do you. Times like this,
I can almost convince
myself I'm speaking
to the previous Lord Gorland.
Your predecessor was also
a man who spared nothing
for the growth and development
of his juvenile form.
Despite the fact that--
[GORLAND]
Yes. Despite the fact
that it was tantamount
to caring for oneself.
An act typically unthinkable
for a Gatlantean.
However, he understood
that he would eventually
be replaced by me,
and that I would have to inherit
the Gorland name and fleet.
[ZURVIVAL] Sir Noll has
inherited your form splendidly--
[GAIREN]
It's a mysterious thing.
Gatlantis has no concept of
father and son, yet they speak
of their successors as if
they were their children.
We may be artificial life,
but having been created
with human-like intelligence,
perhaps these instincts
are an inescapable
byproduct of our design.
If this is true, then one
is forced to wonder if--
[ZWORDER]
Silence, Gairen.
[ZWORDER] Infinite power
springs forth from Terezart,
and its source, Teresa,
is within our grasp.
Once we have her, all that
we wish for will come true.
Everything that comes before
that is a mere diversion.
And what of the ship
that Teresa calls?
Is this Yamato a mere
diversion as well?
[GAIREN] You hoped to prove
that the "love" they claim
to know is no more
than self-serving desire,
and have them destroy themselves
along with the Gamilan fleet,
yet this ship managed
to escape your trap
without sacrificing
a single life.
[ZWORDER]
An act of chance.
Don't give them more
credit than they deserve.
[GAIREN]
There is very little room
for "acts of chance" where
Teresa's prayers are concerned.
After all, it was her prayer
that set these events in motion
when the Yamato answered
the call to come to her aid.
That a pure copy would
infiltrate the crew of
the Yamato is a fortunate turn
we could not have anticipated.
Was this an "act of chance"?
Impossible to know.
I can see the fear you hold
in the back of your mind.
But is it solely a fear of
Teresa? Or something more?
Doctor. I have the results.
Ah. That was quick.
So helpful that you had
your medical certification.
[TOKO] Just from an accelerated
course during the war,
but thanks.
Ohh...
[KODAI]
That bad?
What's that? Oh.
No, everything's fine.
Everything? You're sure?
Sorry. I think Yuki's
just worried about me.
Well, I could give you
some vitamin supplements.
[KODAI]
No, I'm fine. Excuse me.
[sighs]
What exactly is
the problem here?
You're not seriously
having second thoughts
about this mission now, are you?
I estimate we're about a third
of the way to Terezart.
But if we continue
our current course,
we'll be crossing
paths with this...
[SHIMA]
...the White Comet.
[gasps]
[SANADA]
Kodai.
The Gatlantean who was
manipulating that professor--
you said he indicated to you
that the White Comet
was their home planet?
No, not exactly.
That's nice and vague.
[KATO]
But so's everything else,
even the message from
Terezart, right?
It was just the one weird
vision, then nothing since.
[SANADA]
Whatever the case,
even a small risk
of encountering
the enemy's main force on our
own is too great to ignore.
If we want to consider
turning back to Earth
to formulate a new course,
now's the time to do it.
[TODO]
Brave crew of the Yamato,
I commend you on reaching
this stage of your journey.
I will now inform you
of the decision
made by Earth Headquarters.
You are to maintain
your current heading
and gather as much information
on the White Comet as possible,
to determine whether
or not it is
indeed a Gatlantean stronghold.
The discovery of and
arrival at Terezart--
that of course will remain
your ultimate objective.
But more immediately,
we must know what threat
this comet poses.
So you're ordering us
to go closer, sir?
[TODO]
I won't tell you how close.
I leave that to your discretion.
[MORI]
Kodai?
[KODAI]
It's fine.
It's not like the Yamato 's
objective has changed.
We'll continue on,
like we always have.
[DR. SADO] I'm concerned
about our acting captain.
He seems exhausted,
both physically and mentally.
From the time we received
Teresa's message until now,
he's been under
constant pressure
without a moment's rest.
Between his conflicted feelings
about using the Wave Motion Gun,
and the shock of encountering
the Gatlantean fleet...
You're worried he might buckle
under the stress, right?
He may put up a strong front,
but he's really a
sensitive man at heart.
Yeah.
[MORI]
Excuse me.
[BOTH]
Hm?
[HIJIKATA]
Don't mind us.
Kodai's a fighter.
He'll find his way.
But, he's the man you
chose to be with.
You already know that better
than anyone, don't ya.
Yes.
Listen up, there's only one
landing force on this ship,
and that's us.
There's no one to replace us.
So what we lack in
numbers and firepower
we'll have to make
up for with skill.
Huh?
What the hell is that?
[NAGAKURA]
Commander.
[YAMATO CREW A]
Never seen these before.
[YAMATO CREW B]
What are they?
[SANADA] They appear to be
some sort of life forms.
Pending further study,
consider them dangerous.
Ensure that they're not
released from their capsules
aboard the ship.
Sure are pretty to look at.
Shame we can't let 'em out
to brighten things up.
Hey. This is a military
ship, remember?
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Huh? I heard the XO
wanted more samples
so I was just bringing
these to him.
[KODA] I heard it was Chief
Intelligence Officer Niimi.
Hey, hold up--Niimi isn't here.
Oh. Right, she's still on Earth!
Where'd you even hear that
from in the first place?
Oh. Hey, Acting Captain.
Nanbu?
Check it out, fireflies.
I hear we had these on Earth,
too, once upon a time.
Pretty aren't they? Take one.
[KODAI grunts]
[footsteps]
[KAMO]
They're so beautiful.
Huh? What's all the
commotion about out here?
[KAMO laughs]
[OBAMA]
Let's show the others.
Huh. That's peculiar.
[inaudible]
So cool. Takes me back
to when I was a kid.
I can practically taste my
Grandmother's rice cakes.
[KATO]
Tsubasa, Makoto.
Akio, is that you?
[inaudible]
What are you staring at?
[YAMAMOTO]
Uh?
Oh, Lieutenant Keyman.
[DR. SADO grumbles]
Not good. Not good at all.
[TOKO]
What isn't?
These fireflies.
[TOKO]
How so?
[DR. SADO] You haven't felt
anything from them?
No. Why, have you?
[DR. SADO] Huh? Nah,
I prefer to stick to saké.
[WOMAN]
So pretty! Just look at 'em!
Ahh, heh!
Hey, are we sure this is safe?
They said not to let those
things loose, right?
[NAGAKURA] What's up with him?
He's like a zombie.
--[door opens]
--[SAITO] That spineless...
[KODAI]
Captain Okita. What should I--
[thump]
Kodai.
How's it feel being Lady
Luck's favorite captain?
[NAGAKURA]
Hold on, Commander.
[gasping]
Ow, what in the--
Uh. Commander!
[SAITO]
Back on Planet Eleven,
then on Stravase, too.
Dumb luck is all that saved you.
Far as I can tell,
you haven't made
a single smart decision yet.
[KODAI]
You might be right.
[SAITO]
Yeah, so what about next time?
Are you gonna keep puttin'
your half-assed ideals
above the lives of
everyone on this ship?
Then I say turn us around
and take us back to Earth!
Me and my people
want off the Yamato.
Put us on a ship that will
actually fight back!
[door opens]
I don't wanna serve
on a ship of cowards.
[KODAI]
Take that back.
Take it back!
[gasps]
[KEYMAN grunts]
[NAGAKURA]
There you are!
Chief Operations Officer Mori,
this is bad!
It's our Commander and
Acting Captain Kodai!
Kodai? What's wrong?
[SAITO] Maybe you know what it's
like to lose people in battle.
But you have no idea
what we went through.
The hell we suffered down there.
Me, I was lucky.
Old Man Hijikata pulled
me out, saved my life.
For that, I owe him a
debt I can never repay.
But most of our people
weren't so lucky.
Their final moments were
spent waiting for a salvation
that would never come--
crawling in their own blood,
choking on the stench of death.
Go on, take a deep breath!
Even all the way out here
in the vacuum of space
you can still smell it!
[SAITO] All of us who survived
now carry a burden.
The burden of the ones who died.
[SAITO whimpers]
The ones that... they killed!
[SAITO yells]
We survived.
Now it's up to us to settle the
score and avenge their deaths.
We had a chance,
and you let it go!
[KATO]
Hey, that's the acting captain.
Better mind your place, Soldier.
What'd you say?
[KODAI]
Wait.
Leave rank out of this.
[KODAI]
Say what you want about me,
but you will not
disrespect the Yamato.
This is still Okita's ship!
Now apologize!
Yeah?! Or what?
[NAGAKURA]
Have you lost your minds?
[NANBU]
Hey, it's fine. Let 'em fight.
[OTA] Yeah! It'll be good for
'em to blow off some steam.
[AMAGI] That's crazy.
Somebody's gonna get hurt here.
[KURATA] Go on, Commander!
This guy's got nothin' on you!
Both of you, that is enough!
Stop it right now!
[alarm blares]
It's the engine.
The Wave-Motion Core
is becoming unstable.
I'm detecting an abnormal
amount of backflow
coming from the energy
conduction tubes.
That's it.
Try that frequency range.
It's working.
So if we broadcast this
throughout the ship,
we can break the hypnosis.
[SAITO grunting]
What the--?
Now what was I doing...?
[KODAI]
Commander Saito!
It's an emergency!
Take charge here!
Uh, yeah. Leave it to me!
These things...
It's like they're trying
to eat our power systems.
[KODAI]
Sanada!
Kodai! Good, you're here.
Now, Chief. I want you
to start diverting energy
from the Wave-Motion
Coils to the Engine Room.
[TOKUGAWA] That might
burn off the fireflies,
but it's still a big risk.
If they eat through
the conduction tubes
and the pressure drops
it'll be too late. Hurry!
Gauge it wrong, and a
power surge like that
could blow up the ship!
There's no choice. Do it, Chief!
[ANALYZER] Everyone,
please hold your breath now.
Well, that was effective.
[KODAI panting]
Chief! Sit-rep!
[TOKUGAWA] Engine output
holding steady at 50%.
All systems green.
[KODAI exhales]
[DR. SADO] That bug spray
sure came in handy, huh?
[KODAI]
Wha-- Dr. Sado?
That was bug spray?
[DR. SADO] Well, those things
were more virus than bug,
but same idea. [grunts]
I wasn't entirely sure
that it'd work,
but this seemed like a
good time to test it out.
We owe you, Doctor.
[DR. SADO]
Oh, don't mention it.
Besides, you were the one
who neutralized their effects
on our brainwaves, right?
[SANADA]
No. Actually, that was Keyman.
[TOKO]
Was your trick still intact?
I thought I might meet
you if I came here.
[TOKO]
Ahh, such warmth.
[KEYMAN]
What are you doing?
[TOKO]
I'll keep quiet for you.
[GATLANTEAN SOLDIER 10A]
It's happening again!
Cosmo waves emanating
from Terezart!
Hey, Sanada. What's that?
[MORI]
No objects detected on radar.
[OTA] Spatial distortion and
energy emissions increasing!
It could be...
a dimensional projection.
The question is from where.
[SHIMA]
Evasive maneuvers!
No, wait!
Kodai.
Time and space are no
obstacle for communication,
but some things you cannot be
shown until you come closer.
You've risked much and ventured
far based on faith alone.
And as thanks, it is time
that you were offered proof.
[KODAI] Captain Okita.
I'm not good enough.
I've failed to unite the
crew as their commander.
I wasn't even able to keep
your promise to Starsha.
I don't know what to do.
Yamato deserves better.
[OKITA]
Kodai, you're doing a fine job.
[gasps]
Keep at it. You're far
stronger than you know.
Oh, Captain...
Listen to your heart--it will
tell you which course to take.
Wait, Captain, please don't go!
Captain Okita!
[OKITA]
Follow your heart, Kodai.
[SANADA] So this is
what the vision meant.
This is our proof.
Teresa.
Beautiful.
[HIJIKATA]
You realize what you're asking?
What do you say, sir,
will you accept the job?
I fear I'm not
the man I once was.
But yes, I will join
your crew on this voyage.
I've seen the vision,
too, after all.
We all saw it, right?
[KURATA]
Yeah.
Me, too. A vision
of my older sister.
[SHINOHARA] Well I think
we can say you're not just
guests anymore. Welcome to
the crew of the Yamato.
[KATO] What about you?
Who did you have a vision of?
I, uh...
I don't really know, but I
guess I've been called, too.
That's right. And I'll be
counting on your help.
You got it.
[SANADA] You know we
still have the option
to turn back if we want to.
The orders from HQ gave us
wide enough discretion
that we could justify it.
Let's move forward.
There's someone out there
waiting to be saved.
All she has left is a prayer.
But no matter how hopeless
things may seem,
she's still holding
on to the belief
that her prayer can be answered.
Just like humanity
not so long ago.
[KODAI] Set course for Terezart.
We warp in two hours.
I'd expect no less from
your children, Okita.
[GOENITZ] What? We're giving
that man a fleet?
[RAZERA]
Yes, sir.
By order of His
Imperial Majesty.
[GOENITZ] Why? That loser
was practically a corpse
when we found him
drifting through space.
You should know
that in Gatlantis
there is no place for
defeated generals,
and there are no second chances.
It is an exception
that one such as you
is being entrusted with a fleet.
Be grateful to His Majesty.
[ZWORDER]
Sabera.
[SABERA gasps]
Show more respect to the
former ruler of a nation.
[ZWORDER]
You are here because I believe
there's something
you can show us.
Something we have no word
for in our language:
Vindictiveness.
[ZWORDER] To that end, I've
prepared the ideal prey for you.
What do you say,
Supreme Leader Desler?
[DESLER]
I am most grateful.
[SHIMA]
We're surrounded!
[KODAI] Full speed ahead!
Get us out of here!
[MORI]
We're completely surrounded!
[NANBU] Just how big
is this enemy fleet?
[TOKUGAWA]
Open all intake valves!
[SANADA] The Yamato is
about to be destroyed!
[DESLER]
Watch closely.
You claimed that was
your job, didn't you?
I am a man who does
not forget humiliation.