[NIIMI]
I can't believe it.
One of them actually survived.
[RESEARCHER 2A] Their bodies
are frighteningly tough.
I mean, that Gatlantean ship
was smashed to pieces.
[RESEARCHER 2B]
We've found signs
of artificial manipulation
in his DNA.
[RESEARCHER 2A] Are you saying
you think they're not
pure humanoids, then?
[NIIMI] Is it possible that
they're manufactured life forms?
Artificial soldiers?
Didn't you encounter
some of them
while serving on
the Yamato, Niimi?
We certainly did.
Hold on, I'll go get
the research data.
We've confirmed it, Ambassador.
There's a Gatlantean soldier
being held in an Earth
Force research facility.
We have to warn them!
Tell them to stop!
[RESEARCHER 2B]
Capsule pressure rising!
Approaching critical!
[RESEARCHER 2A]
What's happening?
[RESEARCHER 2B]
It's boiling! Pull the valve!
[RESEARCHER 2A]
We're too late!
[PRESIDENT]
People of the world!
Today, as the first President of
the Earth Federation Government,
it is with great honor
and pride that I make this
historic announcement. A new era
of space power is upon is!
The cutting-edge Andromeda-class
ships are now complete!
Peace in space.
That is our ultimate goal.
And the means to realize
and defend that peace
is the strong alliance
between Earth and Gamilas.
As the symbol of assuming
such a responsibility,
the flagship of this
new class, the Andromeda...
[BURRELL]
Why didn't you tell us
that you'd recovered an enemy
survivor from the operation?
[PRESIDENT] ...I have no doubt
her four sister ships
you see here today will
perform just as admirably...
Unless certain
measures are taken,
a Gatlantean soldier's body will
automatically self-destruct.
It's a central feature
of their design.
If you'd informed us
we could have warned you.
With due respect, Ambassador,
if you knew this
about our common foe
then why didn't you share such
a crucial fact from the start?
Are you suggesting that
the fault lies with us?
You should at least have told
us before the joint operation.
We've had some unfortunate
misunderstandings in the past.
But Earth and Gamilas
are supposed to be
allied worlds now.
I can only hope that means you
see us as equal partners.
[TODO] The Earth's population
is still less than a third
of what it once was.
Even though the collapse
of the Desler Regime has
left Gamilas in disarray.
With our skeleton fleet it
would have been easy for you
to invade if you'd wanted.
But I'm sure you'll realize
with these ships that's
no longer the case.
"Jumping at shadows."
That's a saying we have in
the Gamilan language, too.
I must warn you by building this
fleet you're playing with fire.
[TODO grunts]
Among other things,
you've betrayed your promise
to your saviors on Iscandar.
Perhaps. But that was
a verbal assurance
made by the captain of a single
battleship entirely on his own.
It was not a real treaty
and it wasn't the will
of the people of Earth.
[bell ringing]
What's this?
[BURRELL]
The former crew of the Yamato.
We haven't been able
to confirm it yet.
But we think it's possible
they've heard Teresa's voice.
Really?
The Earth's government
has figured it out, too.
I'm going to try and meet
with them directly and talk
before information leaks
from the Gamilas home world.
[KEYMAN] This is the Earthling
who tried to stop
a giant Gatlantean battleship
with one small vessel.
[BURRELL]
If Terezart really is involved,
needless to say this is serious.
Think of what he
might be able to do.
Understood, sir.
Thank you for your
service, Captain.
[MORI]
You get chewed out?
Oh yeah.
"Do you remotely
understand what you did
by going off on your own
like that, soldier?"
"Yes I do. I saved the Earth.
Is that a problem?"
As if I could say that.
Well you can now. There's
nobody's listening out here.
Huh?
Susumu Kodai just saved the
Earth from being destroyed!
[MORI] That's twice now!
A thank you would be nice!
[KODAI]
Hey!
Yuki Mori was so worried!
Susumu Kodai is sorry for that
and will try to
make it up to her!
[laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
[MORI]
Incredible, isn't it?
Sitting here like this,
it's like the Earth
back before the war.
[KODAI]
You remember?
Uh?
Oh. I mean. Sorry.
[MORI]
Are you okay with this?
Honestly?
You're gonna have a
wife who only remembers
the last four years, Kodai.
Doesn't that weird you out?
The way I see it
those are the only
years that matter.
Our trip across the
stars to Iscandar,
and these years that followed.
Maybe they haven't been so easy.
They're not exactly easy now.
But... At least we're alive.
[MORI]
Kodai?
Let's just look to the future.
And find a way we can be happy.
That's our responsibility
as survivors, right?
But Kodai.
Uh?
Fact is, I've been happy
for a long time.
[DR. SADO]
Just look at it, Captain.
A shining, state-of-the-art
city on a beautiful Earth.
[gulping]
[sighs]
Those days fighting Gamilas
for our survival--
they almost feel
more like a dream now.
Well anyway, Captain, drink up.
Today's the third
anniversary of your death.
[DR. SADO]
Earth's already changed a lot.
They've built massive
new cities on the surface
and some ridiculously big
ships with Wave Motion Guns.
Rebuilding is great.
Question is, are we moving
in the right direction.
[cat meows]
The Yamato still has
the Cosmo Reverse System
that saved mankind.
But it already feels
like an afterthought.
Okita...
Maybe we're the only ones
who still remember.
Everything we battled through
and everything we lost.
[SANADA]
Dr. Sado.
--[footsteps]
--Huh?
Oh! So everybody made it, huh!
[KODAI]
Hey!
[DR. SADO] What took ya
so long, ya stragglers?
I'm sorry, Doctor!
Kodai!
[KODAI]
Shima! It's been a while!
I hear you just put on
another big show, buddy.
Everyone's talking about it,
even in the Transport Fleet.
Uh?
[DR. SADO]
All crew, at attention!
Fall in line!
Captain, every crewmember now on
Earth has gathered here today.
They're doing their best
to rebuild in each
of their departments
and fields of expertise.
I hope that gives you peace.
Pay your respects to Juzo Okita,
captain of the Yamato !
Attention!
[YAMATO CREW chatting, laughing]
[SANADA]
Kodai. I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have made you bear
that whole burden on your own.
It's fine.
There's something
nagging at me though.
Right after that incident, there
was communication interference
all throughout the solar system.
[KODAI]
Yeah.
But no one has been
able to explain it yet.
Uh?
[SANADA]
Kodai...
When it happened,
who did you see?
[OKITA]
Kodai, board the Yamato.
[SHIMA]
I saw my dead father.
[gasps]
It'd been ten years
since I'd seen him.
But he was still as tight-lipped
as he ever was.
[TOKUGAWA]
I saw mine, too.
[AIHARA]
That's crazy--so did I!
He was calling out to me,
clear as day.
He said, "Board the Yamato !"
[YAMATO CREW murmuring]
[OTA]
That's so many of us!
Do you think the Yamato 's
former crew
was targeted somehow?
Such similar hallucinations seen
by so many at the same time
obviously poses
compelling questions.
Military command seems to be
investigating it too.
Command.
These new ships with
Wave Motion Guns,
and the aggressive
plans for expansion.
What we brought
back from Iscandar
was supposed to save us,
not make us into some
galactic superpower.
[OTA] It's like the Yamato
called out to us.
Like it's unhappy with
the direction we're headed.
The Yamato , huh.
[MORI] Kodai, who did you
see in your vision?
As for me,
I didn't see anybody.
The Andromeda !
That's the flagship
of the new class.
[NANBU]
You idiots!
[SANADA] There's something
I want the two of you to see.
What is that?
It looks like a comet.
It's an unknown quasar.
We found it during
spatial corrections.
It's actually traveling
toward our solar system,
moving incredibly close
to the speed of light.
Of course it's something
we'll want to monitor,
but it won't reach the
Earth's sphere of influence
for tens of thousands of years.
The far more pressing issue?
The energy waves we think
caused the hallucinations--
we're fairly sure that they
came from the same place.
Exactly the same direction
as that quasar.
The waves were
super-directional,
and clearly pointed at Earth.
So these waves were
aimed at us.
And somehow affected our minds?
And showed us visions
of people from our past?
[SANADA]
Exactly.
And the truth is, the
energy waves were logged
in the Yamato 's
recorder as well.
I managed to take it out before
the military collected it.
I'll display the data now.
[SHIMA, KODAI gasping]
[SANADA]
That's strange.
The data is out of control.
[TERESA]
Warriors of a distant star,
my hope now rests with you.
You saw that, too, Shima?
[SHIMA]
Uh?
Someone was kneeling.
Like in prayer.
Calling for help.
Uh! Sanada, you saw it, right?
They must be asking for us
to go to its origin point.
Here.
[SHIMA]
Look out!
Kodai, calm down.
I have to say I agree with
your assessment, Kodai.
It's hardly scientific.
Still, somehow we've all
been sent these visions.
And our hearts have been shaken.
In my view, we're
being called upon.
To the far reaches of space,
by someone whose very
existence is in peril.
Our hearts can understand
that all too well.
[KODAI]
We should go!
No matter who it is,
or how far away they are!
That's what Captain
Okita was telling me.
I'm sure of it now.
If someone's out there
in space asking for help,
then we should answer the call!
We have to!
Kodai.
[KODAI]
Shima, surely you understand.
A sailor must never abandon
those who are in need of help.
You know your father would
tell you the same thing.
[SHIMA] You're jumping
to conclusions.
We don't have
enough information.
[KODAI] Well, I know this: no
one can fly the Yamato like you!
[KODAI] The original
crew of the Yamato --
hundreds of them--all
receiving the same message!
The military can't ignore that.
If we call on them to act--
[SHIMA] If talking to the
military would make them act,
then I never would have quit.
And don't forget, you're not
on your own anymore.
You should be thinking
about Mori, too.
[thud]
[footstep]
[KEYMAN]
You're under surveillance.
Every person who served on
the Yamato is being watched.
[KODAI]
But why?
I'm fairly certain
you can guess why.
Okay, who are you?
A Gamilan?
[KEYMAN sighs]
This humidity's awful.
I don't know how you
Earthlings can tolerate it.
I'm not asking you to
let go of the past.
I know I haven't. My people
lost a lot in that war, too.
But we Gamilans do owe
the Yamato a debt.
I plan to pay.
[KODAI]
Uh.
I would like you to go
to the moon with me.
[KODAI]
The moon?
[KEYMAN] More specifically
to the Gamilan Embassy.
[YAMAMOTO]
Come on, you guys!
It's been more than 15 seconds.
You haven't even grazed me.
You're making those fancy
new models look pathetic.
You have 5... 4... 3... 2...
[YAMAMOTO]
Time's up.
Tsurumi, you died again today.
[TSURUMI]
Damn it!
[YAMAMOTO]
Instructor Kato
is never going to accept
results like this.
[TSURUMI] Instructor Yamamoto
was one harsh woman.
[PILOT 2A]
What's up with Instructor Kato?
It's his third time
off this month.
[PILOT 2B]
Is his son really that sick?
[TSURUMI] I hear it's space
radiation sickness.
[PILOT 2B]
Inherited?
[TSURUMI]
Yeah.
Makoto blames herself for it.
She said they can slow
its progression some
if he's treated at
the lunar sanatorium.
It sounds like they're
grasping at straws, though.
[chiming]
[YAMAMOTO]
Uh?
Kodai?
[KEYMAN] When the transport
ship reaches lunar orbit,
fake an accidental
fire in the bay,
then drop to the moon's surface
with the purged cargo.
[KEYMAN]
But there's a squadron
of unmanned
counter-terrorist drones
around the embassy,
so stay on your toes.
[KEYMAN]
Meet with Ambassador Burrell,
and you'll learn the truth
behind those visions.
This mission is vital.
It could change the fates
of Earth and Gamilas.
This is just the first step,
so try not to make
any careless mistakes.
This Klaus Keyman.
He's no embassy liaison.
But for right now I just
need to keep moving.
[beeping]
[YAMAMOTO]
Yamamoto of Cosmo Tiger Team
to Lunar Surface Base.
Reporting incursion into
Gamilan embassy airspace
during training.
Notify Gamilans
this was accidental,
and tell them I'm sorry.
[YAMAMOTO]
Stay safe.
[SABERA]
Emperor Zworder,
we may have determined where
Teresa's cosmo wave was sent.
[ZWORDER]
Hmm?
[SABERA]
It is a pitifully remote planet.
However, one ship
from our advance fleet
has vanished while
within its perimeter.
We believe it may be
the home world of the race
who has formed an
alliance with Gamilas.
We've found Earth?
[SABERA] His Imperial
Majesty has decided
the Gatlantis Empire!
Forward!
[BURRELL]
Those called by Teresa.
Surely you found
it suspicious--
how fast they churned
out the Andromeda .
[SANADA]
I'll refit the Yamato.
[KODAI]
That's what you call this?!
[NANBU]
This is not okay!
[KODAI]
Come on! I can't do this alone!