[GIRL 3A cries]
[whimpering]
Hey, honey. Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm all right.
Glad to hear.
But I can't find my brother.
Huh?
Or Mom...
Or my dad.
Don't worry. I bet they went
down to the mine already.
I'll help you look
for them later, okay?
You will?
Yeah, of course.
Now, let's go.
What's wrong?
Yamato.
[NAGAKURA]
Huh?
[NAGAKURA gasping]
[GIRL 3A]
That's my brother's...
[CITIZENS screaming]
[groans]
[FURUHASHI]
All survivors, to the bridge!
[FURUHASHI grunts]
[FURUHASHI panting]
[FURUHASHI]
Hm?
[FURUHASHI grunts]
Commander! It's Furuhashi.
These Gatlantean soldiers--
[SAITO gasps]
[CITIZENS murmuring]
[HIJIKATA] We still have
the means to fight,
and a number of ways we
could make this hard for you.
But we don't want to increase
casualties on either side.
We'll surrender.
Surrender? That word
does not translate.
We admit our defeat and
will lay down our weapons
to end this fighting.
In exchange--
You wish to bring this combat
to an end? Then die.
[COSMODART]
Fight until you die. All of you.
Only that will bring
peace to this planet.
[HIJIKATA] These creatures
are the real devils.
[UNCF OFFICER 6A]
Commander Hijikata.
[ALL gasping]
[SAITO] "Fight until you die"?
That works for me!
But I can't let these civies
get caught up in a war.
That there's our escape plan.
One ship? There's no way
we'll all fit in that.
Maybe you could
send the children.
But they've already
set up a blockade.
You can't do the kind of flying
it would take to slip past
if kids are on board.
Exactly. We'll have to put
all our chips on you.
Huh? Now wait just a minute.
Why'd you pick me?
Don't tell me. This is because
I'm a woman, isn't it?
[SAITO] We're in a lake of fire
and someone needs to bring back
a lifeboat. You're the
best pilot we've got.
[sighs] You owe me, Commander.
[SAITO]
Heh.
I can do this.
[SAITO yelling]
I will...
Go!
[NAGAKURA] I'm not abandoning
them. It's a rescue mission.
[NAGAKURA]
I'll bring back a ship.
I swear it.
[SHIMA] This is the enemy fleet,
as captured by
Master Sergeant Nagakura
before she entered warp.
[KEYMAN]
Gatlanteans.
If they're this far down our
throat in our own system,
how did we not notice?
Hang on. During the war
Gamilas had a supply base on
Planet Eleven, didn't they?
That's right. Since
it's on the far outskirts
of your system we had to
set up an artificial sun.
Since the truce,
the world's been colonized.
Do we know how many people?
Over the last three years a lot
of civilians have settled there.
Apparently it's been
more than 40 hours
since the Gatlanteans ambushed.
The comm channels
are still down.
Oh man. Then what
about the survivors?
[SHIMA grunts]
[TODO]
It's a dire situation.
We never expected that
Gatlantis would advance
into our solar system
this rapidly.
[KODAI]
All right.
Then why are you telling
us to stay away?
[TODO]
It's a significant enemy force.
The Yamato could never face them
alone. It's not your fight.
You are to continue your mission
to Terezart as planned.
But we're the closest!
Uh?
What's the plan for rescuing
the survivors down there?
Trust me. We'll do
everything in our power
Once we've coordinated
with the Gamilan military
we will set out to
retake Planet Eleven
and hope we're not too late.
[SHINOHARA] We'll just pass by?
We're not gonna rescue them?
[KATO] Yeah.
That's the word from the top.
[SHINOHARA sighs]
[KATO] You know I heard this
Terezart mission was allowed
because Gamilas has been
pushing hard for it.
You think that's why the brass
doesn't want us to stop?
I doubt that.
There's a Gammie onboard.
Maybe he's calling the shots.
[SHIMA] Based on our
current coordinates,
this is our shortest route going
full speed ahead from here.
[SHIMA] We've calculated
the origin point of the signal
that caused the visions, and
if we warp every 16 hours
the Yamato can get
there in 29 days.
[KEYMAN] As you can see, Planet
Eleven is a long way off course.
Remember your objective:
Responding to Teresa's call
as soon as possible.
And finding the truth
behind her message.
[YAMAMOTO]
Her message was a distress call.
The Yamato 's objective is
to answer a cry for help.
That's my understanding.
Uh. Hey!
And if we are rescuers,
isn't it contradictory
to simply watch while
our own people drown?
It's not right.
I know you, don't I?
[YAMAMOTO]
Yes, I'm the pilot
whose life you saved,
Lieutenant.
[KEYMAN] Why are you here? This
is for high-ranking officers--
I thought Gamilans and
Earthlings had the same rule.
We don't abandon our own
in times of need.
This may sound cruel,
but it's too late for them.
By now they're probably dead.
We can't know for sure
unless we go there!
We already found one survivor!
[KEYMAN] This argument
is a waste of time.
I'd like to hear the acting
captain's decision.
[KODAI]
Anyone would tell you
charging through their line
would be suicide.
But compared to what we faced
at Balun, it's nothing.
[BOTH]
Mm...
We're gonna learn from
Captain Okita's tactics.
Kodai.
[KODAI] We'll warp out
between the artificial sun
and the surface.
It's too risky!
If we force the Yamato to warp
out that close to the planet,
the damage from the
gravitational forces
will knock the Wave
Motion Engine offline.
We'd need two hours to fix it.
Same for shock cannons
and Wave Motion Shields.
I understand that, Chief.
[KEYMAN] Very bold.
Certainly Okita's style.
But are you certain
this is the right choice?
Should the Yamato
take on this much risk
just to collect dead bodies?
Those colonists made a gamble
when they sent her up--
betting that she could break
through the blockade.
Right.
[KODAI] But they made
an even bigger bet.
That they could survive until
she brought back help.
And if they could believe
in that, then so will we.
All crew, report to battle
stations and prepare for warp!
Begin rescue mission!
We're going to Planet Eleven!
[KODAI] If we can't save people
drowning right in front of us,
how could we hope to
help save the universe?
[KEYMAN] That's not exactly
what Yamamoto said.
Well that's what it sounded
like to me and everyone else.
I'm sure.
Do people become deaf to reason
when they see a
vision from Teresa?
Maybe so. Or maybe...
...it's because
we're on the Yamato.
The Yamato as it is now
has a major weakness.
This isn't like your first trip.
[KEYMAN]
I think you know what I mean.
[door closes]
[KATO]
Say what?
[KEYMAN]
As your advisor,
I can at least try
to mediate the risk.
Huh...?
[KEYMAN] I already have approval
from your acting captain.
[sighs] You heard the man.
Everyone update your call
signs for this mission.
I don't want anyone
accidentally shooting
Mr. Gamilas from behind.
[CREW]
Sir!
What are you planning to do?
Since we've decided to do this,
let's get it done quickly
so we can all move on.
[SAIJO]
Warping in 10... 9...
...8... 7...
[NAGAKURA]
Hang in there, Captain.
And everyone else.
I'm bringing back the Yamato.
[SAIJO]
...1.
Warp.
Warping!
[SAITO grunts]
Well, well.
Thought for sure I was dead.
[TOKO]
Commander!
[SAITO grunts]
[SAITO]
This way!
Commander, look!
Hey, where's the Yamato ?
My brother said it's the best.
He said if it comes
it could take out
these monsters in no time!
It'll come. I am sure of it.
[gasps]
[GATLANTEAN SOLDIER 6A]
Gravitational interference waves
detected. Something
may have warped out.
It's still a little too soon
for the Eighth Mobile Fleet
to have arrived. Show me.
[GATLANTEAN SOLDIER 6A] We can't
determine exact location
inside planet's gravity field.
Order all deployed forces
to search the ground! Hurry!
Survivors are confirmed.
Eliminating the enemy now.
Ha. They came! They really came!
Yamato ...
[KODAI] Shima, can we hover
over that bridge?
There's some strong wind. We'll
need to use the rocket anchors.
Okay, do it. Nanbu!
Sir.
[KODAI] I want you to coordinate
with the soldier down there
to evacuate those survivors.
Bring 'em in fast.
Aye-aye!
Over here! Hurry!
Enemy fleet approaching
from four o'clock, sir!
Here they come... Kato!
Cut off those ships!
[KATO]
Just a few little crabs, sir.
[KEYMAN]
Gotcha.
That Gammie's not half bad.
[SHINOHARA]
Commander!
[KATO]
What's wrong?
[SHINOHARA]
Sorry, one slipped past!
[KATO]
All right, I'm coming.
[YAMAMOTO]
I've got it.
[YAMAMOTO gasps]
[SAIJO] Enemy destroyer
approaching from your six!
All of the evacuees
have boarded, sir.
[KODAI]
Retract the rocket anchors!
Let's get out of here, now!
Damn it. I can't stop it!
[SURVIVORS chattering]
[SAITO grunts]
What's wrong? Feels like they've
got the Yamato on the run!
Surface-to-Air Missiles! Fire!
Type Three... Fire!
[SAIJO] Uh. I'm picking up
something strange in orbit.
There's a large-scale
fold in phase, sir.
What?
[GOENITZ] Almighty Emperor,
ruler of us all,
I come before you with great
humility, to make my report.
As you ordered,
the Eighth Mobile Fleet
has reached the Zol System.
[KEYMAN]
No...
[YAMAMOTO gasps]
What the...?
No. The Yamato !
[KODAI]
How can there be that many?
[SAIJO]
Current total exceeds 15,000.
[SANADA]
That shape. Don't tell me...
[NANBU]
They'll cause a supernova?
[KODAI]
I've tried to do these things
that shouldn't even
be in question.
[SAITO]
Kodai! Fire the Wave Motion Gun!