[SAKI]
Mom? Mommy?
This place is so pretty, Mommy.
[SAKI'S MOM]
Isn't it?
When you grow up, Saki,
promise me something.
That you'll do your
best to be as gentle
as the flowers in this meadow.
[SAKI]
Okay!
[SAKI'S MOM]
I'm sorry.
Saki.
Mommy can't take any more
of this cruel world.
[SAKI]
Mommy!
[SAKI'S MOM]
I'm sorry.
[SAKI] My mother was a kind
person, but she was weak.
[SAKI] If kindness and
humanity have the power
to kill a person,
then I have no need of them.
[OPERATOR 21A]
The Comet Empire has reached
Mars Absolute Defense Zone.
Over 20,000 enemy
ships and counting!
[OPERATOR 21B] We lost contact
with the triple B Fleet
when they executed a short
warp into the comet!
[OPERATOR 21C] Speed of the
Comet Empire's advance
remains steady!
Impossible. They don't
have an unlimited
number of ships
at their disposal.
If we can just continue to
whittle down their numbers
with the Wave Motion Gun
Fleet, we can still win.
Any sign of the Yamato ?
[OPERATOR 21D]
According to the Yamanami Fleet,
which rescued some
of their crew,
there's been no further contact
since they fell
inside the comet.
[OPERATOR 21E]
It's possible that they're...
[SAITO]
Huh? Come again?
[KEYMAN]
A safety mechanism.
If what they say is true, then
the Zemurians had a failsafe.
Some kind of device that would
allow them to enslave Gatlantis.
Permanently, it seems.
So, tell us.
We only let you onboard
to give us information.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20A]
The answer's a secret.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20B] One that
we cannot share with outsiders.
[TOKO]
Give him what he wants.
As the last surviving Zemurian,
I will be listening to
everything you tell them.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20B]
The one that will play
the tune of destruction.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20A]
The cornerstone of control
over Gatlantis.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20B]
The tool of oppression.
[ZEMURIAN CHILDREN] It is
known by the name of Golem.
Interesting.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20A] Golem was
created in the distant past,
by the ancient Zemurians.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20B] If it is
activated, it will bring death
to all artificial life
in the universe.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20A]
When Zworder rebelled,
the very first thing
he did was steal Golem
from the Zemurians.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20A]
However, no matter how he tried,
he couldn't destroy it.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20A] The moment
it senses destruction is near,
Golem will begin to sing.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20B] The tune
it produces is one that leads
to the destruction of
all artificial cells.
[ZEMURIAN CHILD 20A] Throughout
every corner of the universe.
So, you're saying Golem
still exists somewhere.
Tell me where it's being kept!
[KODAI]
Analyzer, what's wrong?
Tch. I guess they're onto us.
[NAGAKURA]
The link cut out? But why now?
[SAITO] We hadn't even gotten
to the most important part!
[TOKO]
I'll tell you.
[OTHERS gasp]
Find Zworder,
and you'll find Golem, too.
[GAIREN]
They've discovered far too much.
[ZWORDER]
In order to devour Earth,
we already knew we'd have
to cast a planet aside.
Eradicate Zemuria.
[ZWORDER]
Is this your guidance?
Is this what you wanted as well?
[ZWORDER]
Teresa.
What the--?
Tectonic shifts occurring
on planetary scale!
Everyone, to your stations!
Yamato , prepare to take off!
Go on, then, attack.
This is an order!
From Defense Command
to all ships!
Fight till the end!
Hold the line at all costs!
If you last a day,
we'll send in the next force.
If you last two, double
that. Three, even more!
As long as we have
the time fault,
Earth's forces
are inexhaustible!
Do not falter! Fight!
Fight for Earth, and for the
children of future generations!
We must not let
our civilization,
nor the human race,
come to an end!
And we shall not!
[SERIZAWA]
We must survive.
No matter what
we must sacrifice.
No matter what we're
forced to become!
[YAMANAMI]
Autonomous control by an AI.
We've finally reached the point
where I'm the only crew member.
[YAMANAMI sighs]
[YAMANAMI]
It's lonely, that's for sure.
Isn't it, Andromeda ?
[CREW 21A] Three Medarusa-
class ships were sunk!
This is just the beginning!
Keep pushing!
Turn the catapult at once!
Prepare to launch
the Deathvatators!
[ALDEBARAN CREW 21A]
Super-massive enemy carrier
has launched scores
of shipborne planes!
Prepare torpedoes,
and multi-launch missiles,
ready to fire!
Follow that with a volley
of graviton spread rounds.
Ready? Fire!
[gasps]
[CREW 21B] Incoming call
from the Aldebaran .
We'll hold the enemy
here for the time being.
Detach your shields and retreat.
Head for the space behind Mars.
We can't. In the name
of our Gamilan pride,
we'll stay and fight!
Detached force inbound.
It's coming directly from Earth.
[gasps]
All ships prepare to
fire Wave Motion Guns.
Fire!
[HIJIKATA] We'll use the
force of the crust shattering
to take off.
Sub-engine starting.
[HIJIKATA]
Kodai, now!
Raise the ship, go!
[SAIJO]
High energy belt approaching!
Yamato , take off!
We've got to get to somewhere
we can communicate
and send information
about Golem to Earth.
Engine! Maximum output!
[YAMANAMI] Now there's
no difference between
Earth and Gatlantis. As long
as the time fault exists,
the killing won't end.
It will go on forever.
[YAMANAMI] In trying to rebuild
our planet, we were confident.
We thought we had
chosen the correct path.
[YAMANAMI] If I can just
destroy that gravity source.
[gasps]
[YAMANAMI]
But that's--
Why would they destroy
their own planet?
[YAMANAMI gasps]
[SHIMA] What did you say?
Hey, repeat that!
[GINGA AI]
Repeating: the exhaustion level
of the Earth-Gamilas
Combined Fleet
has just exceeded 50 percent.
As such, this ship will
no longer engage in battle.
We have received orders from
Command HQ to carry out G Plan.
Henceforth, I will be
assuming partial control
of this ship's operations.
We're under AI command?
What is the meaning of this?
What exactly is this G plan?
Because we have the time fault,
we're able to create an
endless supply of weapons now.
But we're still human,
and we'll reach our
limits very soon.
So, in response,
we'll reduce crew numbers
by substituting AI.
And also, we'll use our
weapons more efficiently
by modifying the human body.
[gasps]
This is war, and if
it keeps dragging on,
then we'll resort to
desperate measures
to ensure the
survival of humanity.
So while we still can,
we're preserving typical DNA.
And if worse comes to worse...
Then we can escape from Earth
in pursuit of other frontiers.
That's the G Plan, isn't it?
How could we do that?
Even if we're carrying
reproductive cells,
producing human beings from
them is a complicated process.
And this ship isn't
equipped for that.
[gasps]
Right. Do you see?
That's why most of the
Ginga 's crew is female.
Fully mechanical production
will be possible eventually,
but it's not at present.
The last bastion of humanity.
Even if we replace
limbs with machines,
our bodies must remain.
If the human race
is to survive--
Do you really have to
take it to such extremes?!
[gasps]
[SAKI]
In order to overcome terror,
we have to become
terror, ourselves.
The Wave Motion Gun Fleet.
Military expansion
using the time fault.
After living through
the war with Gamilas
and all its destruction,
this was humanity's solution.
People are too weak to exist
in such a cruel universe.
We have to evolve.
[YAMANAMI] Priority
Transmission to all ships
from the Andromeda .
Do you read?
I've found the Yamato !
[gasps]
[YAMANAMI]
It was only for a moment,
but I detected her optically.
[YAMANAMI]
It's unmistakable!
The Yamato is still alive!
Yamato .
[YAMANAMI] But they're
caught in the massive
gravitational pull
of the Comet Empire.
It will be difficult for the
Yamato to escape on her own.
Remaining ships,
if you can hear me,
please help the Yamato escape.
[YAMANAMI]
As for this ship,
I'll approach the comet's
gravitational core,
and attempt to destroy the
enemy's source of gravity.
But that'd be suicide!
The Andromeda going in alone,
without any support?
You're right.
With the comet's ability
to control that much mass,
the Andromeda
can't do this alone.
[SANADA]
Captain, may I offer my opinion?
If we were to amplify the
Andromeda 's Wave Motion Gun
using the Ginga 's
Cosmo Reverse,
even that would be
enough to damage
the enemy's gravity source.
[GINGA AI] Achieving the
aforementioned desired effect
would put far too much
strain on the CRS.
We cannot afford to implement
such an unreliable plan
and risk loss or damage
to the Cosmo reverse System
in the process.
I don't remember asking you!
[SANADA]
Captain.
So many.
Too many lives have been
lost in this battle.
It's too late for me to
take responsibility for it.
At the very least...
...I can sacrifice my
life and the Andromeda
for a worthy cause.
I will bring you back, Yamato !
[HIJIKATA]
Yamanami!
[gasps]
[HIJIKATA] Dying is no way to
take responsibility, Yamanami.
[HIJIKATA]
Stay alive.
Stay alive and feel the shame.
No matter how
humiliating it may be,
live through it anyway!
All humans are weak.
We're fallible.
We all make mistakes.
I say, so what?
We're not machines.
[GINGA AI] The G Plan
must always take priority.
[HIJIKATA]
Machines feel no shame.
[GINGA AI]
For the survival of humanity.
[HIJIKATA]
Our inevitable missteps,
and the resulting guilt,
those are the privileges
of being human.
[GINGA AI] This ship will
immediately cease combat oper--
[ICHINOSE]
Captain!
As of this moment,
command AI's been replaced.
I will now take
command of this ship!
Troubleshooting. A-7.
System set to restart.
Ginga ! To the Martian front!
Rapid-fire torpedoes! Fire!
Heh. You are as stubborn as
they come. Right, Andromeda ?
Wave Motion Gun!
Prepare to Fire!
Captain Yamanami.
We'll come with you.
Together, we will survive.
[KANZAKI] Cosmo Reverse
is operating at its limits!
Once we take this shot,
that's the end of it.
It's all right.
This ship belongs to us.
To all of humanity!
Amp factor is 8,000,000 TPA!
Cosmo Reverse, activate!
Wave Motion Gun, fire now!
Rudder's not working!
We've got three more seconds
till the shockwave's passed!
Engine! Maximum output!
Roger!
[SAIJO]
Zemuria is collapsing!
[SAIJO] Rocket anchors have
been forcefully attached.
We're being towed!
[gasps] Is that--?
The Andromeda !
All ships, retreat from
the White Comet at once!
[KANZAKI] The Andromeda
has sustained heavy damage.
She's at her limit.
[KATO]
The Yamato .
She's alive. They got out alive.
[SAKI] Black Bird Team.
All units, take off!
Support the Yamato
and the Andromeda .
Right! Roger that!
Well, I guess this is it.
[gasps] What the--?
[gasps]
[HIJIKATA]
Hm?
[KATO] This is Black Bird
Kato. Do you read?
Successfully rescued
Captain Yamanami.
Repeat: Successfully
rescued Captain Yamanami!
[KODAI] I think that we
should at least attempt
to talk with Zworder
one more time.
[SAITO] There has to be some
way we can cut their strings!
[KEYMAN]
I'm afraid there's only one way.
[SAIJO]
No enemies in sight!
Only the Neu Deusular !
[HIJIKATA]
Keep going.
Ram us in if you have to!