[YUKI]
It'll be a year soon, won't it?
[KODAI]
Mm-hm.
[YUKI]
It almost feels like magic.
[KODAI]
Maybe it is magic.
[YUKI]
Hm?
[KODAI] Think about it,
the Earth came back to life.
The sky, and the sea.
Sometimes I wonder.
All of this...
is any of it even real?
[YUKI] In all the vast
expanse of space,
somehow, we still met,
and here we are, together.
So why not believe that
every single human being
is a part of this great miracle.
A rebirth, just like
the sea and the sky.
We're here because
someone wanted us to be.
[SHIMA]
Kodai?
[gasps]
What's wrong?
Uh, nothing.
Are you sure? You seem kinda--
It's just been a while
since I've seen you.
It's a relief.
[gasps]
[SHIMA]
It's true, isn't it?
She's lost all her memories?
[KODAI] Not exactly. She only
lost the last four years.
But she'll remember,
soon enough.
There you are, Ginga Team.
Hey, the old Antares crew.
Haven't seen you guys in ages.
Welcome to our humble
abode, the Yamato .
I can't believe everyone
in the Air Corps
managed to survive
that situation.
It's a miracle.
So how was it? The Ginga ?
Well, it's practically unmanned,
so no real place for me there.
But how were things for you?
That torpedo bomber?
[SAWAMURA]
I gotta say, it was awesome!
Its turning radius is super
short, and the revolving turrets
have a low rate of movement,
so it's really easy to operate.
Was a bit of
a tight fit, though.
Sounds like you'll
be a dedicated gunner.
Huh?!
So, Shino, where's Captain Kato?
[SHINOHARA]
Hm.
I think, since we're
all here now...
...we should go see him.
[SAKI] We've lost the
Cosmo Reverse System,
and Command AI is gone, too.
At present, carrying out
the G Plan would be difficult.
So, that said, we'll
transfer our equipment
and remain on standby.
We'll await orders.
That's enough, Captain Todo.
I have a lot of questions
about how the Command AI was
damaged, among other things.
But it's wartime.
Let's leave the decisions to
the commanders in the field.
[gasps]
Commander Todo, thank you.
[TODO]
Look.
Earth will soon be facing down
a fight for the mainland.
This may be the last time that
you and I can talk like this.
[TODO] I wasn't able
to do anything for you.
And so, if we live to
meet again someday...
Commander.
[SAKI]
Dad, wait!
I wanted to tell you,
I think I understand
Mom better now.
[SAKI] The only reason humans
tend to be so idealistic
in the first place, is because
of our fragile hearts.
They're so easily broken.
And if they ever hold us back,
then we're better
off without them.
At least, that's what
I've always believed.
But now...
Fate can be odd.
To think you'd be
reunited on Terezart.
[KEYMAN]
My uncle--or, Desler, I mean,
is more than a
power-crazed dictator.
Gamilas is reaching the end
of its life as a planet.
He had to carry that secret
and worry about his
people all his life.
Even if I'd just
learned that much,
this mission would still be...
[BURRELL]
...a happy one.
[gasps]
[BURRELL]
Are you going?
[KEYMAN]
I would like your permission.
[BURRELL] This is a time
of trial for Gamilas.
We must find a new home
with the same environment
and relocate all our
people there very quickly.
I hate to lose such a capable
worker who could assist me
with a project this massive.
But how could I say no
to a look like that?
There's something quite
different about you, Klaus.
Have you fallen in love?
[gasps]
[SAKI]
I've figured it out.
Our tender hearts are an asset.
They're what make us human.
They're inconstant
and uncertain,
but they drive us
to do the right thing,
to follow those tender feelings.
I've salvaged every
part of the Ginga .
That we'd be able
to use, anyway.
I hope you're about to say
I'm the part we could use most.
But you're not
going to, are you?
You know I can't take you.
[YAMAZAKI]
Please, old man.
You've got so much experience.
And these young kids
still have a lot to learn.
Who else could teach them?
I know you'll turn them into
good engineers, Yamazaki.
[SAKI]
That is the essence of humanity,
something machines lack.
We're so strong
that occasionally,
we even destroy ourselves.
It's an awesome source of power,
given only to the human race.
Hijikata. I just wanted to
tell you that you were right.
The Wave Motion Gun Fleet.
If we rely on power alone,
then in the end...
I was only repeating something
I learned from Okita.
But honestly, you're the one
who had your eyes on the future,
on Earth's survival.
You're wrong. I didn't
see the future at all.
That battle begins now.
The battle for the
survival of all humanity.
I feel certain that our
most difficult tests
have only just begun.
I don't just mean you and me,
but the entirety
of the human race.
[SAKI]
That's all I want, to be human.
No matter what awful
fate may await us,
I'm human to the very last.
[alarm wailing]
[PA VOICE 22A] All patients
and personnel must evacuate
the facility immediately...
[TSUBASA]
Are we all leaving the hospital?
[PA VOICE 22A] ...must evacuate
the facility immediately.
This is an emergency...
That's right.
We're all going ahead
to Earth to get ready.
So we can welcome Dad and the
others when they get back.
[OPERATOR 22A]
Fourteenth fleet, launch!
Link up with the
fleet ahead of you
and join the second
defensive line.
We just have to
delay them a bit.
As long as we have
the time fault,
then Earth's forces will be...
Yamato .
[SHINOHARA]
It's not just Tsubasa.
Don't forget you saved
all the other children
who had similar diseases.
Can't you see
that's a good thing?
It's not good.
Betrayal's betrayal.
Don't give me that look, Shino.
Everyone accepted me
without a single word.
I won't die till my debt's paid.
[SANADA] The enemy's defense
is proving overwhelming.
And now that we've lost
the Ginga 's Wave Motion
Core Amplification System,
it cannot be breached.
Not by Earth, Gamilas,
or the two together.
There is a way.
The Transit Wave Motion Gun.
That's right.
If we use the Transit
Wave Motion Gun,
we just might be able
to break through
the Comet City 's Defense field.
We aim for this specific point
and create an opening there.
That's how we can get
close to the enemy.
Then, a suicide squad will head
for the Achilles
Heel of Gatlantis.
The throne from which
Emperor Zworder rules.
And that's where it is: Golem.
Just before she lost
consciousness,
Toko Katsuragi revealed
that secret to us.
Then, we will activate
Golem and make it sing,
and bury every last damn
Gatlantean in one fell swoop.
Kill them all?
They're not human, remember?
I wouldn't let it bug you.
[KODAI]
One more time.
I think that we should
at least attempt to talk
with Zworder one more time.
Kodai.
If we stop once we occupy Golem
and use that to
negotiate with Zworder--
Don't be naive!
Have you already
forgotten the crimes
Gatlantis committed against us?
I haven't forgotten.
And yet, I know his past now.
I've seen what made
Zworder this way
and it's changed things.
I know it won't be
easy to persuade him.
A man who's lived in
despair for 1,000 years.
Even so...
Very well.
If you see an
opportunity, take it.
But also, know when
it's time to give up.
Sir.
Are you okay?
[YUKI]
Why'd he do that?
He faced such opposition,
but still persisted.
He's just that kind of guy.
That's Kodai for you.
The one you knew and loved.
To be honest, I'd never seen
anyone as in love as you two.
It was incredible.
Remember that. I hope it helps.
What'd you say?
The Space Cavalry is being
taken off the mission.
Those are the captain's orders.
Why, old man?
Saito, relax!
I'm afraid Toko Katsuragi
wasn't the only spy
on this ship after all,
and Kato's testimony
proves as much.
The most likely suspect
is in the Space Cavalry
that we brought onboard
at the 11th planet.
We'll have to put
all our chips on you.
[NAGAKURA]
Huh?
You owe me, Commander.
[gasps]
If Toko happens to
regain consciousness,
then we'll question her, but...
What can we do?
How can we cut the strings that
could still be connecting them?
Gamilas is keeping Gatlantean
prisoners, aren't they?
You can stop them all from
self-destructing, right?
[KEYMAN]
Yes, but there's only one way.
Wait, is that...?
[gasps]
Captain Hijikata!
[MIL] When the destruction
of the Yamato is confirmed,
we will arrange for a new place
for the Gamilans to move.
A planet that is
atmospherically similar
to your dying home world.
While the universe may be vast,
we of Gatlantis are the
only ones who can help you.
Are you sure about this, Keyman?
I don't see anything. Perimeter
monitoring shows nothing.
I've no doubt. It was just
a glimpse, but I saw it.
This is a man who claims to
value honor above all else.
Using a move that amounts
to a sneak attack.
Desler must mean business.
We will eliminate the
threat to our safety!
All ships, prepare to warp now!
[DESLER]
Yamato . The great harmony.
High ideals are admirable.
And yet, idealism on
its own will save nothing.
[DESLER] If you possess
the strength it would take
to reshape reality
according to your ideals,
then by all means,
come defeat me, Ranhalt.
Did we succeed?
They're so close!
Core ship, start
emergency purge.
[NANBU]
Enemy ship has separated!
[SHIMA]
What? Prepare reverse thrusters!
[HIJIKATA] No, keep going!
Ram us in, quickly!
[SAIJO]
No enemies in sight!
Only the Neu Desular is visible!
[NANBU] No engine heat detected
from the separated object!
[SAITO] Space Cavalry Team
Alpha, preparing to launch!
[HIJIKATA]
All crew, arm yourselves!
Prepare for hand-to-hand combat!
Chief Tactical Officer Kodai
will lead Team Bravo
to infiltrate the enemy ship!
Lieutenant Keyman will be
in charge of the timing!
Kodai, no.
[NANBU]
No signs of movement onboard.
It seems to be
unmanned, but why?
[SAIJO] Interference with
Wave Motion Shield
detected at ship's rear!
[gasps]
[SAIJO] Part of the Wave
Motion Shield is down!
They're breaking through!
[SANADA] They've broken
through our armor.
Multiple unmanned Gatlantean
weapons are infiltrating!
Team Alpha, focus on
defending the ship!
[SAIJO]
In the front now, too!
[MIL]
So, you removed the core vessel.
In doing so, you halted
the Yamato 's movements
after they charged.
For a spur-of-the-moment
maneuvering decision, stellar.
It's as if you knew
that the Yamato
would come toward us
even before it did.
I'm not surprised your
kind doesn't understand it.
[chuckles]
My nephew's with them.
And family members often
think in similar ways.
Turn left at the corner,
and remember, their
defenses are thick!
Roger that, let's move!
[HIJIKATA] What about the
enemies inside the ship?
[SANADA]
They're dwindling.
It appears as though
Commander Saito's Team
is giving them a good fight.
[KURATA]
Luring them in worked!
They're all yours now, Nagakura!
[NAGAKURA] All right!
Just leave the rest to me!
[SAITO]
One last thing!
Once they've been caught,
go for the elbows first!
[NAGAKURA]
Roger!
[SAITO]
Take that!
[yells]
[NAGAKURA]
Commander!
[SAITO]
Nagakura! Uh!
It's no good.
[NAGAKURA]
Commander! What are you doing?
Beats me!
[gasps]
[ZWORDER]
Love is necessary.
Yes, I have no doubt about that.
It's all so empty.
You shall know despair.
What's that voice?
Could it be... me?
Crying? Him?
It's me... but why?
Please, no. How could I?
[ZWORDER] Without knowing
that you are only
the playthings of fate,
you will go on killing,
and being killed, yourselves.
There'll be no end to it.
You will know despair.
And when it's finally over,
all will be destroyed.
It's human. That drive
to wreak destruction.
Yes, indeed.
Love is a necessary piece.
Not the sort of love that has
the power to save lives.
Nor a love that
can be wiped away
with just a trick of memory.
No, a love that will put
an end to all suffering.
But it can only do so
by bringing about death,
and with it, eternal
rest to all humans.
There is no greater
love in the universe.
So, turns out, in the end, they
were nothing but puppets?
Have they gotten into
the control room?
They're just a few measly rats,
why are you taking so long
to exterminate them?
Leader, Master Ranhalt
is deeply familiar
with the layout of that ship
and poses a great threat.
I'm aware of your orders
that he not be touched,
but the situation is
becoming increasingly dire.
Still, I do not recall
rescinding my original order.
Supreme Leader, at this rate,
your own life is in danger.
I insist on sending
a rescue team--
You arrived sooner
than I expected.
Leader, stop the
fighting at once.
In order to save Gamilas,
you were willing
to cling to Gatlantis.
Isn't that right?
Tell me, why would you send out
a signal to me like you did?
[DESLER]
Hm.
Do you know Zworder's goal?
It is the extermination
of all humanoid life.
Even if Gamilas does
keep their word,
the relationship
is irreconcilable.
You're keeping with
the wrong ally,
and deep down, you know that
it's the truth, which is why--
[DESLER]
Don't deceive yourself.
You would make the same
choice in my position,
but you've let your
time on the Yamato
cloud your judgement.
Uncle.
[DESLER]
Ranhalt.
Don't move.
Supreme Leader!
Now, Klaus Keyman,
assassinate Desler.
If you do, then I promise
that I will save
both Earth and Gamilas.
After all, for clones
such as ourselves,
time's of no
consequence, anyway.
In order to truly exterminate
every last humanoid,
it could take tens
of thousands of years.
[gasps]
[MIL]
A 10,000-year reprieve.
It could be yours if
you do as you're told.
Now, kill Desler and exterminate
the love in your heart!
[MIL] Now, then, young
Desler, choose your fate.
Will you kill him?
[DESLER]
Shoot me, Ranhalt.
[SAITO] Dying isn't the
most difficult thing
that people have to face.
[MIL]
How can you not make a choice?
[KODAI] No, Keyman!
You can't make a choice!
[KEYMAN]
Kodai!