[static]
[KODAI]
This is Susumu Kodai,
Acting Captain of the
Space Battleship Yamato.
We don't want to keep fighting.
We want you to peacefully
withdraw from this system.
[MAZER]
Yamato. Damn that Yamato !
[crash]
We have no chance of
reinforcement or resupply.
If we keep advancing like this--
[MAZER]
We will chase them down!
That Earthling vessel beat us.
Yet they refused to claim
victory and put us to the sword.
Until we sink that ship,
as warriors, we can neither
die nor truly live.
Even if it means disobeying
the emperor's orders,
and burning in the fires of hell
for it, we have no choice!
All we can do is fight!
[MIL] "You are here to
show us vindictiveness."
Do not think
Emperor Zworder meant
he wants that trait
for our kind.
Such emotions of the humanoid
species are corrupting to us,
and work like a powerful drug.
In fact, we are
seeing its effects
on the Gatlantean mind now.
Driven by hatred for the Yamato,
they are chasing
her against orders.
And thus, they're contaminated
and threaten his perfect fleet.
They are waste.
Which must be purged.
[DESLER] Mil, just to be clear,
I came all this way
because I was told I could
battle the Yamato.
Yes, of course.
How you treat the source
of the contamination
is your choice.
I accompany you merely to report
what I see to the emperor.
[DESLER]
Hmph.
[GAMILOID 11A]
Ten seconds to warp out.
Prepare to fire
the Desler Cannon.
[MIL] We are not ruled by
the emotions of the individual,
which is precisely why we were
able to rise up and thrive.
To be honest, I don't like
being around you humanoids
and your lowly pursuits.
[GAMILOID 11A] Desler Cannon
energy charge: 120%.
I'll be the first to admit that,
at times, we get carried away.
[DESLER] Driven mad by our
emotions. By love, most of all.
No, but why?!
[GOENITZ] The contaminated
fleet has been purged
by His Excellency, Lord Desler.
It would appear he has
passed his first test.
Is this a good faith attempt to
repay his debt to the emperor?
Or does he obey merely
because he understands
he has nowhere else to go?
[ZWORDER] Do not try to
explain him with logic.
Keep watching,
and soon you shall see
that which defines and
shackles them all.
[SHIMA]
What is it? Anti-matter?
[SANADA] No. Its characteristics
are similar,
but this is something else.
Some unknown form of energy.
Interesting.
And you picked it up
in Teresa's communication waves
from that last broadcast?
Yes, and that's
not all we found.
There was a vast
quantity of data
our systems were able to decode.
Information on Terezart.
These schematics show complex
gravitational interference
fields around the planet.
And beyond that, a defensive
armada of heavily armed ships.
And here's another model
embedded in that broadcast,
which our computer just
finished decrypting.
[OTA]
What is that?
[SANADA] Terezart is completely
encased in solid rock,
with a composition
starkly different from
the planet itself, suggesting
it was brought in later,
from one or more
other celestial bodies.
[NANBU] What sort of technology
could do that?
[SANADA] Furthermore, there are
indications of enemy strongholds
throughout this rock encasement.
[SAITO]
You don't say.
According to this data,
Terezart itself is hollow,
with incredibly high
levels of energy
in that space beneath
the planet's surface.
That unknown energy is
flowing in from a dimension
other than our own. It's hard
to say where it's coming from.
Teresa.
[SHIMA gasps]
But with that shell...
[SANADA]
Even if we make it there,
direct contact might
be impossible.
[MORI]
No...
Then how are we
supposed to save her?
[HIJIKATA] The enemy's
defenses look strong.
Even landing on Terezart could
prove incredibly difficult.
To pull this off, we'll need to
combine the Yamato 's power
with the mobility of the Space
Cavalry and Air Corps.
But that still may
not be enough.
We should ask ourselves now,
are we willing to use
the Wave Motion Gun?
XO. This unknown energy.
Is it showing a declining trend?
Yes, sir. If we posit that this
massive rock encasement
is a structure designed to
extract Terezart's energy,
then what we're seeing
all makes sense.
The energy of Teresa?
So Gatlantis is taking it
for themselves, like fuel?
[HIJIKATA]
There may not be much time left.
It's your call, Acting Captain.
How do you want to fight?
What do you want?
Oh, when I want something,
you'll know.
I was simply thinking about what
you did to the Yamato 's engine.
So tell me, why did you
stay on this ship?
I stayed for the warmth.
[TOKO]
Who is it? Me?
Enemy fire from 4,
7, and 11 o'clock!
AA combat! Open all gun ports!
Starting evasive
maneuvers! Hold on!
More missiles headed
our way, three o'clock.
[SHIMA]
Are we surrounded?
[KODAI]
Any ships?
[MORI]
None in radar range.
Use angle of fire to estimate
number and positions
of enemy ships.
Raise the shields!
[MORI] Missiles concentrated
at five and seven o'clock!
Shima, full speed ahead!
Get us out of here!
Strange to fire so many
missiles outside radar range.
[GAMILOID 11A]
Target increasing speed by 70%.
Distance from transfer
point expanding.
Transfer temporarily suspended.
[DESLER]
Quick and decisive.
It seems that battleship
hasn't changed one bit.
Watch Mil.
I'm about to show you
something rather interesting.
Keep your eyes on the space
around the Yamato.
Heh. Instant Matter
Transfer Device.
Re-compute target points.
Missiles from all directions!
They still have
ships ahead of us?
There's no way! We should've
shaken 'em all by now!
Maybe they have a second line?
Just how big is
this enemy fleet?
It's as if the enemy
could anticipate
exactly which way we would move.
[MORI]
We have missiles approaching
from every direction.
We're completely surrounded!
Acting Captain,
what's your plan?
We're calculating
an escape route now!
[ANALYZER]
Calculation is complete.
In 18 seconds, there will be a
six-second opening for escape
at one o'clock and 16 minutes.
You realize that
could be a trap.
[OTA] I can't get a stable read
on the post-warp coordinates!
Shima!
Aye-aye, sir!
Wave Motion Engine.
Output to maximum!
[KODAI]
Emergency warp!
Warping!
[GAMILOID 11A]
Target has entered warp.
They saw a gap and
they seized on it.
Finding a sliver
of hope in the dark.
That's the Yamato for you.
[SHIMA]
Warp complete.
[OTA] Radar and scanners
coming up empty!
Hey, Kodai. Do you feel that?
Yeah. Like before.
It would seem we've been pulled
down into a dimensional rift.
[KAMO]
Chief, the wave coefficient
is stuck in alignment!
And the energy conversion
rate is still accelerating!
What? Is the pressure reduction
unit malfunctioning? Check it!
No, that's not it.
Quick, Chief. Shut down
the engine, now!
[TOKUGAWA]
What?
The Yamato is about
to be destroyed!
Stop the engine, hurry!
[KAMO]
Stopping engine, sir!
[KODAI]
The remnants of a supernova?
[SANADA] Yes, this space
is filled with it.
High-energy atoms with
accelerated electrons
and protons are
causing a rapid chain
of particle reactions
all around us.
The Wave Motion Engine is
constantly taking in energy
from the vacuum of space.
If it does that here, and
continues energy conversion...
...it would trigger a reaction
that would blow the Yamato
apart from the inside.
[CREW gasping]
To put it in laymen's terms:
We're floating inside
a powder keg.
And it's like our
engine is a match.
[yelps]
Where's the enemy?
Radar's still down!
[NANBU] Shouldn't the enemy's
radar be down, too?
We need to move! We can still
use the sub-engine, right?
Yes, Admiral.
Nanbu! Load the
rear torpedoes!
Prepare for suppressive fire on
the acting captain's command!
[NANBU]
Roger that!
[KODAI] Shima, evasive
maneuvers to starboard.
Fire!
[GAMILOID 11A] Internal engine
pressure rising rapidly.
Same is true for
Lascaux-class ships.
Continued fire is dangerous.
[DESLER]
Tell them to keep firing.
[MIL gasping]
[DESLER]
I'm impressed.
[MIL gasps]
That's a neat little
trick you have.
It works not only
at vast distances,
but through different
types of space as well.
That's the advantage
of the cosmo wave.
Thanks to that, we've had no
trouble tracking the Yamato
across the stars.
At least so far.
[DESLER]
Higher-dimension
communication
utilizing telepathy.
[MIL gasps]
[DESLER] If I recall,
the prayers of Teresa
have been described
that way, too.
[NANBU] They're attacking
like their weapon systems
aren't affected in here at all!
[TOKO]
Why don't you answer?
What? That's new.
The enemy fire is
completely missing now.
[gasps]
[GAMILOID 11A]
Internal explosions
due to excessive
energy conversion.
Like your great leader,
Emperor Zworder.
You seem to be a special
sort of Gatlantean
with extraordinary skills.
Perhaps that spy who's
infiltrated the Yamato is, too.
[SHIMA]
What is that tube structure?
[SANADA]
It's clearly been constructed.
[AIHARA]
Some undiscovered alien race?
[SANADA] No, the style
is remarkably similar
to ruins of the Aquarians.
And if it was built by
that advanced civilization,
there's a decent chance
it houses technology
that could help us.
Risky, though.
Let's go! Set a course
inside the tube structure.
[DESLER] I'm guessing
that glowing object
is the source of this
dimensional rift.
I'm also guessing
as we draw nearer
its even affecting your
dear cosmo waves.
[gasping]
And now that mental trick you're
so proud of no longer works.
We'll have to turn to a
more conventional method.
And what is that?
[DESLER grunts] We're going
to search with our eyes.
A waste of effort.
Those telepathic waves
won't reach your emperor
from here either, Mil.
[BOTH gasping]
Whatever that tube is,
we're in it now.
[OTA]
That's strange.
This structure's interior
seems to be composed of
a different dimensional stratum
than the space outside.
Is that even possible?
Two clearly separate
dimensions.
Seamlessly connected
by a solid structure.
[HIJIKATA] XO. If that's true,
isn't it also possible
we could use this to get
back to ordinary space?
Yes, sir. However...
[DESLER] The many technological
achievements of Gatlantis,
and its unique philosophy
are delights to behold.
And yet, I wonder...
Who among the vassals
truly understand the
heart of their emperor?
Even as it sullies his people,
to him it may be like a
fragrant, intoxicating wine.
Or perhaps it's a
favorite plaything.
I would venture your emperor
does not actually desire
the destruction of that ship.
The Yamato and her crew are
most likely piquing his interest
in a way he hasn't felt
in a very long time.
Surely your clever liege must
have realized it from the start.
They are things that I want
but the Yamato 's survival
means nothing to me at all.
[MIL gasps]
If you don't mind, I'll hold
on to the gun from now on.
[HIJIKATA] We'll release Wave
Motion Energy into this tube.
Then draw the thermal
radiation it creates
back into the Wave
Motion Engine.
Stimulated emission?
It's a way to use this tube's
structure to achieve warp.
But one wrong move, and the ship
will be to blown to pieces.
We're floating in gunpowder,
then striking a match
on purpose, hoping we can
harness the energy to escape.
It's up to me and the chief.
We'll each carry half
of the burden.
No. We all will.
We'll carry it together.
And we'll carry it now because
there's no time to waste.
[MIL] You were planning
this all along.
You steered them to this place
to cut off our telepathy,
didn't you?
[DESLER] I am a man who
does not forget humiliation.
[MIL]
You must realize it.
What will happen if you
use that weapon here.
[DESLER]
Space itself will burn.
The Yamato and those
ships entrusted to me
will share the same fate.
Desler, no!
[DESLER]
Watch closely.
You claimed that was
your job, didn't you?
Reading extra-dimensional
implosion!
[CREW gasps]
[OTA]
But how?
Hold on. The approaching
Wave Motion Energy
is colliding with this space
in the way we theorized,
with a shockwave of radiation.
Kodai!
If we raise the gravity anchor
and absorb that shockwave,
then we should be
able to reach warp
without firing the
Wave Motion Engine!
Roger. Shima, do you think
you can ride that wave?
The reflection rate
won't stabilize in here!
Aligning with center
of emission!
[MORI] Stimulated emission
wave approaching!
[SHIMA]
Inertial canceler to maximum!
Contact with our stern!
It's pushing us!
[TOKUGAWA]
Open all intake valves!
[KODAI]
All crew, brace for warp!
[SHIMA]
3...
...2...
...1...
...warp!
[GAMILOID 11A]
The Yamato has jumped.
Just as fortuitous as always.
[SHIMA sighs]
We made it.
[exhales]
[CREW sighing]
[DESLER]
Without its core,
this dimensional rift
should soon disappear.
[gasps] What are you planning?
Calm down.
Without the interference
from that core,
your cosmo waves
should return to normal.
I'm surprised that
doesn't make you happy.
[MIL growls]
[beeping]
Supreme Leader,
the entire military has
been awaiting your return.
As loyal as always.
You have my gratitude.
Garle Desler!
[gasping]
Tell me, Mil. What do you
think of my actual fleet?
Of course your emperor
will learn eventually.
[MIL whimpering]
But still,
there's no need to rush.
[MORI] You could take command.
You basically did today.
Today I helped us fall
in an enemy trap.
I was simply cleaning up
my own mess.
[MORI]
But, Kodai... I know.
You'll say the same
thing he did.
"We'll carry it together," huh?
Yes, "We'll carry it together."
He's mature, when he's
concerned about someone else.
[MORI]
Huh?
[HIJIKATA] I understand
why you're worried.
Kodai is facing a steep wall.
It's daunting.
But he has to learn
to climb it himself.
The best thing you can do is be
ready to catch him if he falls.
Your parents believed in
and supported each other,
all the way to the end.
I know you two can do the same.
That's what humans always do,
when we're at our best.
Yes, sir.
[TOKUGAWA]
I've analyzed the data.
When we used that
shockwave to warp,
we achieved three times
the usual output.
Have you been able to figure
out what caused the collapse
of that dimensional rift?
[SANADA] There's a signature
in the neutron fluctuations,
something we've seen before.
Most likely...
The Desler Cannon.
[ZWORDER]
I've grown tired of seeing it.
[OTA]
The White Comet has vanished!
[TOKO] Do you love him?
Is that what drives you?
[KEYMAN]
Kodai, she made her move!
[KODAI]
Is that it? So it's true.
[NANBU]
It's the home base of Gatlantis!
[TOKO]
You're willing to kill me?
[HIJIKATA]
Full speed! Prepare to warp!