Mother...
[gasps]
[MIL] What's the matter?
Why aren't you shooting?
Did you not hear me
say that I would save
both Gamilas and Earth?
[ZWORDER] Mil. Just what
do you think you're doing?
[MIL]
I only wish to see for myself.
Your memories, before you
spent a thousand years
smoldering in despair.
How easily people adapt
their fragile feelings,
simply to pursue their
short-term interests.
[MIL] I was born to be emperor,
and I will fulfill my destiny.
Every word that I speak
comes straight from Zworder.
[MIL]
Now then, Young Desler.
Make your choice for the future.
[DESLER]
Shoot me, Ranhalt.
[gasps]
Mil isn't lying,
everything he says is true.
And I think you ought
to be cognizant of that.
If you belong to the Desler
family, don't hesitate!
[KEYMAN gasps]
[DESLER] No matter what
you have to sacrifice,
do what you must to succeed.
Leader.
[KODAI]
Don't do it!
[KEYMAN gasps]
[KEYMAN]
Kodai?
[pants] This is the exact same
test that I was given before.
Whether you decide to
pull the trigger or not,
you're going to lose something
that's important to you.
You must not choose.
[DESLER]
As soon as you do, you've lost.
It's the truth.
That's enough!
[MIL, ZWORDER]
How can you not make a choice?
--[gunshot]
--[YUKI gasps]
[MIL groans]
[AIHARA] Small-sized unmanned
enemy weapons have gone silent!
I guess that means the
assault team succeeded.
[NAGAKURA panting]
Commander.
[MIL] Hmph. I suppose it's
all the same, ultimately.
The being at the end of the
barrel may have changed,
but the fact you'll choose
to pull the trigger has not.
I see. Because I'm human?
And we have always made
the choice to shoot?
Although, there's never
been any other option.
Even if it meant
breaking our own hearts.
We've chosen to live,
let others live.
And that's the way
it's always gonna be.
We'll have to kill for survival.
[KODAI]
But there's a price.
Sooner or later, we'll have
to pay for our crimes.
When that time comes,
someone has to die.
[MIL gasps]
And I wish to volunteer.
If it will bring about
peace, I surrender.
I offer myself to your people.
[MIL chuckling]
[MIL laughing]
[SAITO]
Fine. Take that.
Go ahead and make
me self-destruct.
Even if you do it right here,
you might as well be lighting
a little firecracker in space.
I'm sure you still don't get it,
but dying is far from
the most difficult thing
that people will
face in their lives.
And out here, I won't be
causing anyone more tro--
[NAGAKURA] Idiot! I won't
let you die like this!
All alone out in space?
That's giving them
exactly what they want!
Back off!
Are you stupid? Come on!
They'll take you down with me!
[NAGAKURA] Let 'em see
what happens if they try!
I won't allow those people
to destroy anything!
Not the Yamato or Earth,
and I won't stand for
them breaking your heart!
[NAGAKURA crying]
You see, Commander?
Even a hard-ass like me--
I couldn't bear it.
Dying alone.
[NAGAKURA] And I refuse
to let it happen to you.
You've got to keep doing
whatever you can to stay afloat,
and only die when
you know it's over.
If you can't die with
dignity, then you've lost.
[NAGAKURA sobs] You deserve
better than that, Commander!
You can't give up!
[MIL] Do you presume you're the
first to make such an offer?
[MIL]
Every civilization has one.
A fool arrogant enough to
believe they can end it all.
Can you guess our response?
What we've done to
every would-be savior
who made that same mistake?
[DESLER]
If you are truly his friend,
then you must not shame him.
[KODAI]
Even so, here I am.
Someone has to initiate peace.
Somebody has to take the risk
and refuse to pull the trigger.
[ZWORDER] So you won't
pull the trigger, you say?
[ZWORDER] If that strategy
worked in this world...
[ZWORDER]
...then who would suffer?
The decision has
already been made.
[MIL, ZWORDER] And you must
pay with your blood!
[gasps]
[KODAI gasps]
No.
[KODAI]
Yuki.
Yuki!
Come on, stay with me!
[KODAI gasping]
It's okay! Yuki!
Why now?
[KODAI]
Yuki!
Kodai... I...
But why? Tell me!
I don't know.
[YUKI]
I have no idea why.
But I'm... glad...
[MIL]
What's this?
You were supposed to
have lost your memories.
You shouldn't remember,
and yet...
...you still act
like you love him.
[MIL] Once, you said
feelings aren't real.
That they're just electrical
impulses traveling along
pathways in the brain.
And giving these mere
compulsions names
like "heart" and "soul"
is only a futile act the weak
engage in for momentary comfort.
[MIL] But there is still
something we cannot yet
conceive of,
and humans possess it.
[ZWORDER grunts]
To be forced to
inherit the memories
of all previous generations?
What a fate.
One shared by all Type-Zworders
who have been saddled
with such high-
functioning brains.
So, let's hear them.
Those words.
Perhaps they are the very
thing you have been waiting
thousands of years for.
This body is no more
than a container.
[MIL]
A "soul"?
There is such a force
that cannot be described
by any other name.
And it is tying people
together even now.
[MIL]
With a strength akin to gravity.
I have no doubt.
Emperor, could it be
that you were not aware?
Even though we
inherit the memories,
each generation of Zworder has
differed slightly from the last.
And we from Gatlantis,
we are also humans
with individual souls.
Our lives are tied together,
linked by bonds,
woven with love.
[MIL]
I want to know your reasons.
There is still too much
we haven't yet learned.
About Earthlings, yes.
But about ourselves, as well.
It is too soon to
make a decision.
[MIL] I believe that
if we can start over,
if we can end a thousand
years of despair
and turn our eyes toward
a different future...
...we'll change things.
We'll find a way,
and I will also choose
not to pull the trigger.
[gunshots]
[ZWORDER gasps]
[TOKO gasps]
Mil, no!
[GAIREN screams]
[coughs]
[gasps]
[BODYGUARD 23A] Supreme Leader,
are you all right?
[BODYGUARD 23B] The
reinforcement fleet is arriving!
Hurry!
He's gone.
This is such foolishness.
[TOKO crying]
[HIJIKATA]
We had a once-in-a-lifetime
chance at peace,
perhaps bestowed upon
us by God himself.
But in the end, it was wasted.
The battle will proceed.
What has been set into motion
can only play out
to its conclusion now.
[DR. SADO]
I...
[KODAI] If only we had met him
under different circumstances.
[TOKO] We cannot choose
how bonds connect us.
I need you to help me.
I won't speak in platitudes.
You and I both know
how this ends--
In one side's destruction.
[KODAI]
Even so,
we can try.
If we want to carry the
hope young Zworder gave us
forward into the next chapter,
we must act now.
You're going, then?
I'm bound to this cause,
and I will fight for
the future of humanity.
I can't sit idly by.
[KEYMAN] I wish to leave the
future of Gamilas to you.
[KEYMAN]
On a new planet,
with a new heart that
understands the futility of war.
I implore you,
guide our people well.
Give this message to Kodai:
My Neu Deusular
will fight for him.
I swear I will
protect the Yamato
from the Transit Wave Motion
Gun's energy radiation.
I urge you to persist.
[DESLER]
Why did we choose to fight?
[DESLER] Why didn't we try
to love one another instead?
[beeping]
[KEYMAN]
Hey. What's--?
[KODAI]
What happened to you?
[SAITO]
Nothing, calm down.
I just took a relaxing
little bath, that's all.
[KODAI]
What's this about? Tell me!
It can't be!
[KODAI] Does this mean...
you were one of Gatlantis's...?
[SAITO] This is pretty much
the only way, right?
To cut a puppet's strings and
separate him from his master?
How long did you stay in there?
Heh. Don't worry,
I'll last long enough
to help you win one battle.
Tch.
[alarm ringing]
[AIHARA]
Urgent call incoming
from the Gamilan
forces near Mars!
The Warp Interference
Field's gone!
The White Comet is
heading for Earth!
[GOENITZ]
Greetings, Earthlings.
I have wonderful news.
We of Gatlantis have chosen
not to destroy Earth,
in light of your
intrinsic value.
We welcome you and
your planet to be absorbed
into the glorious realm
of the Comet City Empire.
The time fault is wasted
on your kind, I'm afraid,
and it can only be used at its
full power once it has been
fully integrated with
the Ark of Destruction,
a formidable weapon
that only we possess.
[CITIZENS murmuring]
[GOENITZ] Never again shall
this planet bask in the light
of its star, the sun.
Both land and sea will
dry up, and become barren,
unable to support
any form of life.
Therefore, the entire human
race will be sustained by
Gatlantean charity alone
for the foreseeable future.
Breaking news:
the Comet Empire has issued
a demand for
unconditional surrender--
[ALL gasp]
[MAN 23A]
What the--?
[GOENITZ]
All shall revere the emperor.
If you value your lives,
you will remain loyal.
[GOENITZ] And only those
who have demonstrated
significant capabilities will be
allowed to live on as slaves.
[BOY 23B] Hey, what
happened to the Yamato ?
The Yamato will come.
It'll take those bad guys
out for us, right? Right?
[MAN 23D]
Hey, wait.
The Yamato . Yeah, that's right.
They'll save us!
[WOMAN 23C]
Didn't they already sink?
[MAN 23E] Not yet. They weren't
listed among the sunken ships.
So, I guess they're
still afloat.
[MAN 23F]
Then they're alive? Really?
That's right, as long as
we've got the Yamato ,
then there's still hope.
Yamato !
[YUKI] We are born alone,
and we will die alone, too.
So why do we even meet at all?
[HIJIKATA] Kodai,
the next captain of this ship
must be you.