Huh?! The engine! It's stopped!
[HIJIKATA]
And the sub-engine?
[TOKUGAWA]
No good! Not responding.
[HIJIKATA] All hands, prepare
for emergency landing.
Emergency landing
in four, three, two, one.
Landing!
[CREW grunting]
[KODAI grunts]
[KEYMAN]
I'm sorry, but I must.
[gunshot]
[KODAI grunts]
[SANADA]
Klaus Keyman.
I wonder... who is he,
ultimately?
Was the Gamilan Ambassador
who invited Kodai to the moon
nothing more than a spy
from the very beginning?
Who knows?
It seemed as though Desler's
appearance was a surprise
to Keyman, as well. But, still.
Why was he aboard the Yamato ?
[KEYMAN]
I am just like you.
I can't allow the earthlings
to take control of
Terezart's power.
That's why I chose to accompany
them, to neutralize
the Yamato at the
appropriate moment.
[DESLER]
Thereby bringing
the power of Terezart
back to Gamilas.
For those who resist
democratization,
and fight to restore the Desler
regime to its former power.
Heh...
[gasps]
[DESLER]
It's been a while. Hello, Mil.
There seemed to be quite a bit
of commotion outside earlier.
[DESLER]
Oh, yes.
Some outlaws attempted to
steal the emperor's treasure,
but it was nothing to
be too worried about.
I simply punished them
and took it back.
[gasps]
Which means Terezart
is now under
the absolute control
of our fleet.
[gasps]
[DESLER]
The door is open.
You may see for yourself,
if you'd like.
[DESLER]
Seeing is your job, after all.
Now that it's ours,
I wish to enter
into negotiations
with Emperor Zworder.
I will humbly offer
Terezart to the Emperor.
And in exchange...
[KEYMAN] Do you think they'll
agree to negotiate with you?
Emperor Zworder does not
strike me as the sort of man
to be preoccupied
with appearances.
When he considers the
possibility of losing Teresa
along with her planet,
if they fight us,
I'm sure he'll hear our demands.
The discovery of a planet
where we Gamilans can live,
or the creation of one.
Gatlantis may be able
to achieve that.
[DESLER]
Ranhalt.
Sir?
[DESLER] What kind of ship
would you say it was?
An unusual vessel.
And its crew was a little
strange, as well.
They weren't like soldiers.
Seemed more like pilgrims,
if you ask me.
[DESLER]
Pilgrims, huh?
[GENERAL 16A]
What of Master Ranhalt?
Has he arrived on Terezart yet?
[GENERAL 16B] His bloodline
is blessed with great fortune.
[GENERAL 16C] Is it true?
Does Teresa really exist?
[KARZET]
Yes. The Gatlantean forces
occupying the planet
were all but eliminated.
Tides have turned.
Terezart is now
under our control.
Our fleet has control?
What's their attachment?
[KARZET]
Supreme Leader Abelt Desler.
[GENERAL 16A gasps]
[GENERAL 16B]
What? Does this mean he's alive?
[KEYMAN] The head of
the Deslerists is unknown.
It's been a mystery for years.
I haven't a clue who
he might be, either.
I'm sure he'll
show himself soon.
At this stage, whoever
it is has no other choice
but to contact me directly.
[TARAN]
Supreme Leader.
There's a call for you
from the mainland.
It can't be!
[GIMLEH]
Garle Desler.
Greetings. I'm glad
to find you well.
I never imagined I would
see you alive again.
Hello, Gimleh.
[GIMLEH] As the dictator went
mad and tried to destroy
the Yamato,
the Capital, Baleras,
became caught in the crossfire.
This is the defamatory tale
the Democrats are espousing,
just so you're aware.
However, I know the real story.
You only took that route to save
both Iscandar and Gamilas.
It was an act of necessity.
Baleras Tower.
It was a blade pointed
directly at Iscandar.
Those who stole
the Cosmo Reverse,
and plotted against you,
even if only to save Gamilas
from the path of ruin,
still built that massive weapon
without your
permission to do so.
Thus, the military betrayed you.
You, who had discovered
their intentions,
made use of
the Yamato 's attack,
and cut the ship that served
as its source of energy
free from the tower.
[GIMLEH] Then, in order
to effectively wipe out
the traitors, you destroyed
the second Baleras.
[GIMLEH] And I know that you
did it all to save Gamilas
and bring peace to Iscandar.
If we are to ensure
Gamilas's future,
then a powerful dictatorial
regime is our only option.
When you were presumed dead,
I thought that Master Ranhalt
was the obvious choice
to take your place
as dictator, but then,
much to my surprise, I learned
that you were alive and well.
So, Ranhalt.
Yes?
Tell me. Do I have
your blessing to rule?
Uh. Yes, of course.
Very well, we shall inform
the people at once
of Supreme Leader Desler's
victorious return.
Preparations for the
uprising are complete.
I hope you will come back
as soon as possible.
They're no better than vultures.
[TOKUGAWA]
That's right.
As far as we can tell,
it's not a mechanical failure.
I have no idea what
the underlying cause is.
Although I think it's probably
safe to assume it can only
be an issue with the Wave
Motion Engine itself.
[SAWAMURA sobbing]
[cries]
[SHINOHARA]
It's so surreal.
His body is lying right there,
but Tsurumi is gone now.
Where do we go from here?
Teresa.
[KEYMAN]
I just don't know anymore.
The preparations are complete.
My next steps have already
been decided. But...
Teresa.
If you really are a goddess
who can see to the end of time,
I beg you to come to my aid!
Which path is the
best for me to take?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[TERESA] While aboard
the Yamato, you had
intense feelings, and
they were all correct.
What is best is always
subject to change.
Depending on the
choices you make.
Do not act in accordance
with your thoughts.
Take action from
your feelings instead.
For you are part of
the great harmony.
Great Harmony. Me?
[DESLER]
What are you doing here?
[KEYMAN]
Supreme Leader.
Might be embarrassing.
But that title is one that
you must have been seeking
for quite some time.
Heh. If Teresa were
the sort of being
one could take from this place,
I might think you were trying
to betray me by coming here.
And you, then?
What brings you to her?
[DESLER]
Likely the same thing as you.
Everyone has something they
use for emotional support.
Especially if they've
lived most of their life
relying solely on
their own power.
And yet this support
upon which I relied...
She swooped in and
took a planet from us.
One we were attempting to
remake from the ground up
to create a new home
for our people.
We planned to migrate
there and begin a new life.
[KEYMAN]
You wanted to save Iscandar.
And so...
[DESLER] The Cosmo Reverse
is not all powerful.
And our planet is not Earth.
I am not certain whether
even the Cosmo Reverse
can save Gamilas.
And that is why
I sought a new frontier in
the far reaches of space.
However, the end result, heh,
I don't have to remind you
what that was.
At that time
what was I trying to destroy?
Supreme Leader Desler.
Oh, well.
Whatever my reasons, the fact
remains that I tried to get
a large portion of our
population caught up in it.
And for that sin,
I may never truly atone,
no matter how I try.
In the future, if the people
of Gamilas decide to trust
another Desler with the
honor of ruling over them,
it can only be you.
[gasps] Do you mean...?
Forgive me.
[TERESA] Deep within your heart,
you will always find love
for someone other than yourself.
You continue to treasure them,
more than you value
your own life.
And as long as you
have that feeling,
you are qualified to rule.
You have the strength
to lead your people,
and it stems from your selfless
love for another being.
[chuckles] And you love to
answer questions no one asked.
[TERESA]
It's complete.
It appears all the
bonds are in place.
[gasps]
Teresa?
[BURRELL]
Secretary Hyss. Just now
we received communication
from Lieutenant Keyman.
[HYSS]
And did he learn anything?
He did, about the plot
to restore Desler.
The man leading that faction
is former Director-General
of the Imperial Guard,
Heydom Gimleh.
It's Gimleh?
I didn't know he was alive!
On the honor of the Security
and Intelligence Bureau,
I promise I will arrest him!
[KEYMAN]
If I keep my emotions...
Uh? Uh!
[SAITO] Hey! Gammy! What do
you think you're doing here?
[KODAI]
Stop it, Saito.
[grunts]
How can I--
How can we believe what you say?
[KEYMAN]
You can't. Words from the mouth
of an undercover operative
shouldn't be trusted.
Undercover?
Bureau of Security
and Intelligence.
Internal Investigations Unit.
That's who I work for.
We're going back to the Yamato.
If you're going to
kill me, do it later.
[DESLER]
Rebellion?
[TARAN] It seems Master Ranhalt,
who was returning ahead of us,
released the Earthlings
without our knowledge.
[DESLER]
Let him do as he pleases.
The Yamato, too.
I can't quite figure out why,
but it just ignited out
of nowhere. It's odd.
It's nothing to celebrate until
we know a little bit more.
We may have to give
the order to abandon ship.
We can't. We'll fly as we are.
Shima! Prepare to
initiate launch!
Uh. Roger.
Hey, Chief. That all right?
[TOKUGAWA]
Do what you want!
[KEYMAN] Ambassador Burrell
came up through Intelligence,
and he believes
democratization is needed
to build a future for Gamilas.
I was working under his orders
to expose the mastermind
who's trying to restore
Desler to power.
But you're part of his family.
Yes, all the more reason.
I wish to leave Gamilas
a true democracy.
You see, it's the least I
can do to atone for the sin
of being born the nephew
of a tyrant.
[KODAI] So, then, the reason
you boarded the Yamato,
and helped us make
it to Terezart...
[KEYMAN] I did it all as a
way to win Desler's trust,
and get closer to
the architect of the plot.
And my plan was a success.
But then, Desler himself
showed up unexpectedly.
Why don't you just go with him?
[beeping, door clicks]
[KODAI]
If this rumor about Gamilas
being close to the end
of its life is true...
[KEYMAN] Oh, yes.
That was an option, too.
However, the goddess
told me something.
[gasps]
[KEYMAN] Don't think, take
action from your true feelings.
[AIHARA] Incoming call from
XO Sanada! Everyone is safe!
[HIJIKATA grunts]
Get in there already!
[gasps]
[KODAI]
Keyman!
[KEYMAN grunts]
Yamato, take off!
[SHIMA]
Deploying main wings!
[MIL] It seems you, too, chose
to do something unexpected.
[KEYMAN gasping]
That impulsiveness
and emotionality
will destroy the universe!
And yet... my emotions also
give me the power to do this.
Damn you!
[groaning]
Are you sure you're
okay with all this?
[KODAI] This is Kodai.
We've lost track of Keyman.
Are you able to trace
him on your end?
[AIHARA] He withdrew
from the enemy ship
and then took a sudden dive.
We've lost his signal.
What'd you say?
[AIHARA]
Yamamoto is currently in route
to investigate his status.
[KEYMAN]
Is this it, then?
[KEYMAN gasping]
[KEYMAN]
I was alone for so long.
[KEYMAN] And, alone,
I was able to do anything.
But now, that's changed.
[gasping]
[KEYMAN]
Mother.
One more time.
[YAMAMOTO] I'll save him,
no matter what!
Huh?! There he is!
[YAMAMOTO] This is Yamamoto.
I've got Lieutenant Keyman.
Have a medical team ready.
What the--?
What the hell's going on?
Teresa.
Yuki? What is it?
Teresa said, "Don't forget
what I told you."
[TERESA]
I bid you farewell.
All of you. The time has
come for me to return
to where I belong, but
I will continue to pray.
However, I do not pray
solely for one planet,
nor for any particular
people, either.
Of course. I should
have known we couldn't
keep her in our
clutches for long.
[TERESA]
Planet to planet. Time to time.
And also, person to person.
The field of life is held
together by bonds of love.
[TERESA] The power that
supports the universe.
[MIL]
What is this? It can't be.
[gasps] Is this Teresa's...?
[TERESA] I entrust my wishes
to the ship of Great Harmony.
And, as I said,
I will continue to pray.
[KODAI]
Bonds.
The love of the universe.
I suppose this will do.
[HIJIKATA] We were entrusted
with a prayer, and that means
we must do everything
we can to stop Gatlantis.
For all the life in
this universe,
I cannot exaggerate
what's at stake.
So, reverse course, and
full speed, on both sides!
Yamato, we now set
our course for Earth!
[MIL]
Defeat the Yamato.
[GIMLEH] If this continues,
Gamilas will be ruined!
[DESLER]
Who are you? Tell me.
[KEYMAN] All the same.
I am nothing but a traitor.
[SHIMA]
What is their ultimate goal?
[KODAI]
The elimination of all life,
and that includes themselves.