[ZWORDER]
The universe is infinitely vast.
[ZWORDER] An endless
expanse of silent lights.
Stars die,
and new stars are born.
An eternal cycle of life.
Yes. The universe is alive.
It lives.
It lives!
[ZWORDER] And that is why
we will show it our love.
[MEN groaning]
[groaning]
[ZWORDER]
Empty.
Truly empty.
What meaning was there
in these men's lives?
[ZWORDER]
To what end did they serve?
What imagined purpose
could possibly justify
such needless suffering?
[MEN screaming]
[ZWORDER] Love is the only
worthy aspiration.
A love which can purge
every last bit of suffering
from this universe.
An infinite love!
[ZWORDER]
Wouldn't you agree...
...Teresa?
[TERESA] Everything has
been predetermined.
But... that does not
mean all is lost.
Warriors of a distant star...
my hope now rests with you.
[UNCF OPERATOR 1A]
All ships have warped out.
Assuming deep battle formation.
[UNCF OPERATOR 1B]
Prepare for ship-to-ship combat.
[UNCF OPERATOR 1C]
Open data link.
All radar operators monitor
for changes in grid display.
[SERIZAWA]
It has been 60 days
since the enemy occupation of
the floating continent began.
The Gamilans have determined
that the base staff
is already lost.
They are now prepared to launch
a full-scale assault to expel
the Gatlantean Fleet from the
Eighth Floating Continent Base.
Earth Fleet will have
the honor of assisting
the Gamilans in this endeavor
to reclaim their facility.
The Gamilan force will
attack as the vanguard.
We will bring up
the rear to defeat
any and all enemy ships
that slip past them.
Happy hunting.
[AIHARA] Armored Assault-type
Zoelguut-class vessels.
Even on Gamilas, it'd be rare to
see three together in one place.
Gather all the intel you can.
Let's see if we can
size up their defenses
while we have the chance
to see 'em up close--
[KODAI]
Aihara.
Gamilas is our ally now.
We didn't come here
to spy on a friendly fleet.
[AIHARA]
U-Uh. Yes, Captain Kodai!
Taking support position behind
the Zoelguut-class vessels.
[beeping]
[UNCF OPERATOR 1A]
The enemy Gatlantean Fleet
is deploying units
at all positions
on the Eighth
Floating Continent.
They're advancing
to our front...
[UNCF OPERATOR 1B]
Transmission received
from patrol and
surveillance unit:
"Warning. Multiple firepower..."
In position. Combined Fleet
is prepared to engage.
Roger that. Let's stay sharp.
Make sure there are no surprises
waiting for them out there.
[UNCF OPERATOR 1C] First contact
with enemy unit imminent.
Preparing to engage.
[UNCF OPERATOR 1A]
Earth Fleet advancing.
[UNCF OPERATOR 1D]
The fleet has begun the attack.
[MORI gasps]
[UNCF OPERATOR 1C]
Taking heavy losses!
[UNCF OPERATOR 1B]
Enemy advancing.
Second wave incoming.
[TODO]
Hm? What ship is that?
[UNCF OPERATOR 1C]
ID confirmed:
Ship K-47 of the 2nd Destroyer
Escort Fleet... the Yunagi.
[MORI gasps]
[RADAR OP. 1A]
Fighters launching from carrier!
[KODAI]
Topside missiles... fire!
[KODAI] Torpedoes at the ready!
Tubes one through four!
Angle of aperture,
three degrees! Fire!
Captain! Enemy fleet retreating!
They're pulling back to
the floating continent.
They're what?
They had us outgunned. Why
would they suddenly run away?
[RADAR OP. 1A] Gamilan
fleet appears to be pursuing.
Open a line to
the Gamilan flagship.
Get me their captain.
On it.
[RADAR OP. 1A] Reading a
massive, unidentified object
approaching the
Gatlantean fleet!
What?
Uh. What the hell is that thing?
A ship?
It's enormous.
[RADAR OP. 1A]
The forward Gamilan fleet
has been completely wiped out!
[UNCF OPERATOR 1A] 6th and 7th
squadrons taking heavy losses!
Have them pull back at once!
Commander. I believe this
could be... an opportunity.
[TODO]
Hm?
Ensure that no friendly vessels
will be caught in the
line of fire. Not one.
Then, you may proceed.
Sir.
Priority command for
all deployed fleets!
Initiate Plan A!
All remaining ships, fall back
to designated positions.
Plan A?
What is that?
I don't know.
Looks like these were
encrypted files
pre-installed on
the fleet network.
But this is... It can't be!
[COUNTDOWN]
24... 23... 22...
...21... 20...
...19... 18... 17...
Orders for Plan A:
2nd Destroyer Escort Fleet
retreat to third warning
line immediately.
[NANBU]
First I've heard of this.
[COUNTDOWN]
...9... 8... 7...
...6... 5... 4...
...3... 2...
...1...
[RADAR OP. 1A] Reading extra-
dimensional energy emissions.
[gasps]
Uh. Wave Motion Gun?
[NANBU]
Yeah, but, who fired it?
[STARSHA]
Promise me you will be better.
[KODAI gasps]
[STARSHA]
Promise me you will be better.
Swear that you won't ever repeat
the same horrible
mistakes we made.
[OKITA]
I give you my word.
[KODAI grunts]
[SANADA]
Kodai, we have to face reality.
The Earth was nearly
wiped out in the last war.
If we're going to survive...
[YAMANAMI] All ships, this is
Earth Federation Defense
Force Fleet Flagship, Andromeda.
Destruction of the 8th Floating
Continent has been confirmed.
We will now transition
into a mop-up operation.
Earth-Gamilan Combined
Fleet vessels,
remain on guard until
we give the all-clear.
We of course applaud you for
your efforts to this point.
Is this for real?
This has gotta be some
kinda sick joke, right?
The Andromeda.
So it's already been completed.
[UNCF OPERATOR 1A] Andromeda now
entering the combat area.
Very impressive.
The Dispersion Wave Motion Gun.
After our success here today,
perhaps the people of Gamilas
will begin to see the
Earth in a new light.
No doubt.
Your enemies will, too.
[ANDROMEDA CM 1A]
Enemy battleship spotted.
Dead in the water.
[UNCF OPERATOR 1A]
Defiance and Saratoga
unable to continue
operations due to damage.
They are requesting permission
to return to Earth via
long distance warp.
Permission granted.
[MORI]
A Wave Motion Gun.
[TODO]
Hm?
[MORI]
You built a Wave Motion Gun.
How could you?
Is this how we honor the promise
we made three years ago?
[ANDROMEDA RADAR OP. 1A]
Enemy battleship's engine
has just fired up!
Main gun, lock on target!
[ANDROMEDA RADAR OP. 1A]
It's accelerating too quickly!
[YAMANAMI] Belay that order.
Rear guns 3 and 4--fire!
Fire!
Gatlantean vessel closing
on us at high speed!
What?! Veer hard to port!
[KODAI grunts]
[YAMANAMI grunts]
You're sure about that?
[YUNAGI RADAR OP. 1A]
Yes, sir! The enemy vessel
followed the same trajectory
as Defiance and Saratoga.
Emergency warp, now!
We need to get back to Earth!
[KIRYU] Enormous mass warping
out in outer lunar orbit!
What?
[KIRYU] Confirming Saratoga and
Defiance 's warp out signals
from the same point.
Object is thought to be
the Gatlantean battleship
that warped from
the combat area.
[SERIZAWA] What about
the defense satellite?
[UNCF OPERATOR 1A]
Automated intercept has engaged!
[UNCF OPERATOR 1D]
Defense line has been breached!
Gatlantean vessel...
now within lunar orbit!
Will enter Earth atmosphere
in 400 seconds!
Where is the projected
landing site?
[KIRYU gasping]
It's here!
[SERIZAWA gasps]
So this is how Gatlantis
fights their battles.
[OBSERVER 1A]
Mr. Serizawa.
Please compose yourself,
sir, there is no time!
Quickly! Give the order to
evacuate the capital region!
[SERIZAWA]
It's hopeless.
If something with that much mass
comes down at that speed,
we're all doomed.
Now Issuing the alert
for the civilian evacuation
guidance program.
Open all passages into
the old underground city.
[KIRYU] New warp out signal
detected near enemy ship.
[KIRYU]
ID K-47.
The Yunagi !
Kodai's here?
[NANBU]
Enemy ship overhead!
[AIHARA] It's on course
to hit the atmosphere!
Main cannons at the ready!
Fire!
[NANBU] No effect! We just
don't have enough firepower.
[KODAI]
Disengage!
Huh...?
Helm! Drop us down
directly below their stern.
[KODAI] We're going to
push up on their keel
to knock them off course.
Thrusters to maximum!
[gasps] Yunagi , they've just
rammed the enemy ship!
Be careful, Kodai.
It's no use! We can't change
their line of descent!
[AIHARA]
Captain, incoming call
from Lieutenant Mori
at HQ on a coded channel.
From Yuki?
[AIHARA]
Connecting.
[MORI] Kodai, listen,
I'm patching you through.
Captain Kodai.
Wait, Sanada?
[SANADA] Send us the enemy
vessel's course data.
[KODAI]
Are you sure about this?
We'll only have one chance.
[UNCF OPERATOR 1A] Evacuation
of third block is underway.
Seventh block is released.
Lowering platform now.
Break away. Reverse thrusters.
[NANBU]
Aye-aye!
Once again we'll have to
trust her to save all of us.
[YAMAZAKI] Attention: all
workers in dock, board ship
or take immediate shelter
in the evacuation block.
This is not a drill. I repeat,
all workers in the dock,
board ship or take immediate
shelter in the evacuation block.
[DOCK WORKERS chattering]
[ENOMOTO]
C'mon, c'mon! Move it!
[TOKUGAWA] Auxiliary engine
system check complete.
Holding charge at 100%.
Circuits closed. Main cylinder
primed and ready.
Start auxiliary engines.
Starting auxiliary engines.
Connect heavy power lines.
Energy output at maximum.
Weapons systems prepare to fire!
Rotation constant at 1600.
Igniting auxiliary thrusters.
Dock gantry locks, released!
Let's go, men. Raise her up!
[SANADA]
Angle of fire 35 degrees.
Fire!
We... We've been saved.
Uh. Status report!
Oh, yes sir!
Enemy battleship
disappeared from radar
at an altitude of 18,000 meters!
They really did it.
[KODAI]
Sanada.
[UNCF OPERATOR 1D]
It's the Yamato, sir!
That shot came from the Yamato !
Is that possible? I thought
she was being remodeled.
Get the undersea dock
on the line!
Yamato.
[KODAI, NANBU, AIHARA gasp]
[TOKUGAWA, SANADA]
Huh?
What the...?
What is this, what's happening?
[KODAI]
Uh. Captain Okita!
[OKITA]
Kodai, board the Yamato.
Board the Yamato.
[SANADA]
In my view
we're being called upon.
[KODAI]
We should go!
[KODAISHIMA]
And don't forget--
you're not on your own anymore.
[MORI] Fact is, I've been
happy for a long time.
[KEYMAN]
Meet with Ambassador Burrell
and you'll learn the truth
behind those visions.
[KODAI] But for right now,
I just need to keep moving.