[ZWORDER]
Sabera. The Silver Priestess.
[ZWORDER] A unique
and irreplaceable being,
separate from we of Gatlantis.
To do something so unrefined
to a treasure like you.
[TOKO]
It is nothing.
[TOKO] If I can be of
service to my emperor,
then I don't care
what happens to me.
[TOKO]
My name is Sabera.
The one and only.
She who pilots this
Comet City Empire.
Its only priestess.
[organ plays]
[TOKO gasps]
[organ continues]
[TOKO gasping]
[TOKO gasps]
[TOKO]
The Desler Canon?
It's similar to the
Wave Motion Gun.
During our recent battle,
inside that alternate dimension,
we picked up readings
that matched it.
If Gatlantis has one--
a working Desler cannon.
[TOKO]
Wait. Why tell me?
[gasps]
[KEYMAN] On this ship,
what other option do I have?
What do you want from me?
[KEYMAN] You're the one who
started this, remember?
If we speak openly,
we'll each become
the only one the
other can rely on.
You must agree that
has some value.
[TOKO]
The only one.
I wonder about that.
[gasps]
Uh?
[KODAI]
Any luck?
[KEYMAN]
Still working on it.
[SHINOHARA]
Word is, the enemy knew
our exact position
in that last battle.
So the higher-ups think
someone on board
is being controlled by them.
Like that Professor
What's-his-name
on planet Stravase.
Okay, but why would
they think it's one of us?
Planet Eleven, that's why.
We spent all of that
time off the Yamato.
Okay, by that logic,
what about that medic lady?
Toko Katsuragi?
[SAWAMURA] I can't believe
we have a mole hunt
just when we're about to
reach the White Comet.
[TSURUMI]
That's a mystery, too.
There's no proof it's
the enemy base, right?
Proof, huh?
[CREW gasp]
Still a bit choppy.
But at this distance
this is the best optical
data we can capture.
So that's it.
That's the White Comet.
[gasps]
[GOENITZ]
Desler's betrayal...
The emperor was able
to foresee it?
[SABERA]
Naturally. The eyes of Zworder
reach Gamilan hearts, too.
He knew Desler would be
misled by his emotions,
and risk his own forces in his
attempts to defeat the Yamato.
[GOENITZ]
But how shall we proceed?
No matter how valuable
a sample he may be,
now that we've lost
contact with Mil.
[ZWORDER] I care not. Let the
madman do as he pleases for now.
We've already absorbed
the energy we need.
Terezart has provided
for us quite well.
We will continue our plan
and set course for Earth.
To the home planet of the
vessel called by Teresa.
That pitiable world
predestined for destruction.
[ZWORDER]
I've grown tired of seeing it.
[glass shatters]
[TOKO]
What?
[YAMAMOTO]
Katsuragi, what happened?
I'm just clumsy.
Do you need something?
Ensign...
[YAMAMOTO]
Akira Yamamoto.
That's disappointing. The enemy
mole doesn't remember my name.
What is that, a joke?
[YAMAMOTO]
Didn't sound funny to Keyman.
I know that you're a spy.
[YAMAMOTO]
Don't move.
What, you're not gonna deny it?
If the Lieutenant says
I am, it must be so.
Because after all, we have
been open with each other.
[YAMAMOTO gasps]
Ahh!
[YAMAMOTO groaning]
I think it's rather cute--
you trying to stop me.
[YAMAMOTO muffled groans]
[TOKO] Do you love him?
Is that what drives you?
[YAMAMOTO muffled groans]
[TOKO] Pathetic,
what it makes people do.
[gun clicks]
[KEYMAN]
That's enough.
[YAMAMOTO grunts]
Kodai, she just made her move!
--[alarm blaring]
--[footsteps]
[KODAI] Attention, all crew. Arm
yourselves and stay on alert.
We are closing the bulkheads.
Toko Katsuragi is on the run.
She may be working
as an enemy spy.
If you see her,
report to the bridge.
This is nuts. Could she
really be behind this?
And be careful.
If she's Gatlantean,
there's a risk
she'll self-destruct.
[TOKO panting]
[TOKO]
Your imperial majesty...
It's me...
[TOKO]
...the Silver Priestess.
The only one who can pilot
the Imperial Star Gatlantis.
[TOKO panting]
[KURATA groans]
[KURATA coughing]
[NAGAKURA groans]
[SAITO]
You okay?
[NAGAKURA]
Commander.
[scraping, bang]
[SAITO]
Dammit.
Sorry, she got away from us.
We're reviewing the footage
from all the ship's cameras now.
She can't hide for long.
[OTA] What the...?
The White Comet has vanished!
[KODAI] But how?
What could explain that?
[OTA]
I don't know.
All I can tell from the
data is... it's gone!
[creaking]
Now what? What's that shaking?
Engine room!
Gravitational interference
waves detected at 12 o'clock.
Kodai!
We need to pull a 180.
All crew--
[CREW grunting]
[ZWORDER laughs]
We're being pulled in!
Anomaly on gas cloud surface!
What?!
[MORI]
Core of comet emitting
powerful gravitational
interference waves!
[CREW gasping]
This can't be natural!
It's like it's
targeting the Yamato !
They must have some way of
controlling this super gravity.
So it's true. It's the
home base of Gatlantis!
[SANADA] Those waves
are like solar flares.
Even with the Wave
Motion Shields,
a direct hit could cripple us.
[TOKO] This feeling again...
What's it mean?
[organ plays]
[TOKO]
That music. Who's playing it?
Our Silver Priestess at work.
Doing that which
no one else can.
[TOKO]
I am... Sifar Sabera.
In Gatlantis, where new
generations are born
through cloning, I am unique.
[SABERA]
The Yamato.
That ship which
leads hearts astray
and threatens misfortune...
for all of Gatlantis.
[TOKO] You must know I'm here.
You're willing to kill me?!
[organ continues]
[SABERA]
You!
You who calls out to me
from that vessel.
Who are you?
My name is Sabera.
Nonsense! Sabera is my name!
I am the Arbitrator!
She who coaxes the Comet
City Empire to move!
I am she who realizes the
commands of the great emperor.
[SABERA]
I serve His Majesty.
[TOKO]
Who are you?
Who else would I be?
[BOTH]
My name is Sabera.
The one and only.
Gravitational interference
waves weakening!
Do it, Shima, now!
What is that?
[GAIREN] The two Saberas
are resonating, sire.
We were careless. We have
never let this happen before.
Two pure copies,
in such close proximity.
Emperor. What is this?
These pure copies.
They are not like us, sire.
For two to exist
simultaneously...
[ZWORDER grunts]
[TOKO gasps]
[TOKO]
Emperor...
[footsteps]
You must not doubt the
uniqueness of your being.
My liege?
You are the only humanoid fit
to judge your own kind.
[SABERA gasping]
Time for you to know
that you do not follow me.
For the truth is
that I follow you.
Last of all humanoids--
the great Sifar Sabera!
[organ plays]
[CREW gasping]
[organ continues]
[TOKO]
Emperor...
Why can't I hear you?
Well, go on. Do it, Klaus.
Pull the trigger.
[TOKO] Shoot me before I'm
captured, and forced to talk.
[TOKO, KEYMAN grunt]
[TOKUGAWA]
Maintain maximum output!
Too late! We're being pulled in!
We're going into the center
of the White Comet!
[KODAI gasps] Are those
what I think they are?
[MORI]
It's a large enemy fleet!
Shima!
It's no use! We can't stop!
[gasps]
That's odd. Why aren't
they attacking us?
[GAIREN]
How can this be?
The resonance between
the Saberas
has silenced the entire fleet!
Then the time has come.
Prepare Comet for phase
transition dimensional jump.
[ZWORDER]
Sabera, what's wrong?
Sabera...
Sabera!
[gasping]
[TOKO]
What have you done?
You should have killed me,
but you saved my life.
Yeah, yeah, I know. It's absurd.
[TOKO]
This emotion.
I felt it with him, so long ago.
[SABERA] And it doomed
us both to suffering.
An anguish we could
never escape.
[SABERA]
Yet it felt so enticing.
A warm and beautiful pain.
[ZWORDER]
Sabera.
[GAIREN] I fear there's nothing
more you can do, Your Majesty.
The two of them are
locked in this resonance.
If it continues...
[ZWORDER]
Get out.
[BOTH]
Uh?
[ZWORDER]
I said out! All of you!
[TOKO]
This feeling...
What is it?
This is love.
That force that made us suffer.
Zworder and me.
Why must you repeat it?
[SABERA]
My Emperor... My Zworder.
[ZWORDER]
You are the Silver Priestess.
[SABERA]
I am Sifar Sabera.
[ZWORDER] You should know
more than other beings
that love is what leads
your species astray.
[SABERA]
Yes. I do know love.
As do you.
[ZWORDER]
No!
Gravity source determined.
Now we can see what's
pulling down the ship.
Transferring analyzed image
over to main screen!
[MORI] Diameter near
68 hundred kilometers.
Roughly the size of Mars.
That's the core of
this comet? A planet?
Is that it?
Their world... Gatlantis?
[SABERA] Let us stop this.
I've told you many times before.
You need to confront
what's in your own heart.
Say no more.
What you seek to destroy
is not out there,
it is not the universe.
[ZWORDER]
Silence!
It is deep within yourself.
[ZWORDER grunts]
--[ZWORDER grunts]
--[SABERA gasping]
[gasping]
Gravitational waves are gone!
Full speed! Prepare to warp!
Warp!
Warp complete, sir.
Engine readings look good.
Gatlantis clearly had
the power to destroy us.
And yet for some reason,
they didn't attack.
Who can say, but one
possible explanation is
they decided that a lone
battleship is of no consequence.
[ZWORDER] Gairen, you will
produce a new priestess.
[GAIREN]
How many is this now?
We put strict limits on
what we copy to her brain.
And yet, somehow she
keeps regaining them.
The memories of the original.
I've reported the situation
to central command,
and they agree that we
must keep moving forward.
We've seen with our own eyes
the power of Gatlantis,
and can't let them get stronger.
We'll make our way to
Terezart and set it free.
[TOKO] Because eventually,
you'll betray the Yamato.
[KODAI] Do they not have
ideals where you're from?
[NAGAKURA]
We'll hit 'em hard and fast!
[YAMAMOTO]
Tsurumi! Watch your tail!
[TSURUMI] Damn. Until the
Yamato gets here...
[KEYMAN] Either you find
a way to bear this burden,
or the Yamato has no future!