[SERIZAWA]
For the past several days,
Gatlantis has been making
moves that warrant attention.
Pluto, Neptune,
and the asteroid belt.
They have been
appearing repeatedly
across our entire solar system.
Engaging in hostilities with
our forces, then retreating.
But this, I've no doubt
it's just a diversion.
The only possibility is
that they're preparing for
a large-scale invasion of Earth.
Allow me to present my evidence.
But how can an object
the size of Jupiter
simply warp in like that?
And when exactly did it arrive?
Is there any way to
negotiate with them?
Their sole objective
is destruction.
The statements made by refugees
from the eleventh planet,
currently being held
on the moon,
make that abundantly clear.
For Gatlantis, the concept
of conquering other cultures
and then integrating with them
to expand their own
power does not exist.
Well, then, in that case...
We cannot avoid combat.
[SERIZAWA] We are using the time
fault factory at full capacity.
But, even so, we still don't
have sufficient numbers.
To support further increases,
it will be necessary
to implement a system
that unites the government
and the people.
The Wave Motion Fleet
was the subject
of intense criticism. Both
internally and externally.
And now, we will
put it to the test.
In the war with Gamilas,
humanity was pushed
to the brink.
We stood on the very
precipice of extinction.
And this time...
...it's even more urgent.
We must act as soon as possible.
If not, it will be too late.
CR amplifying system,
confirming power!
Roger. I'll refit that,
along with the Wave Motion
Reactor Core's amplifier.
[NIIMI] This is the foundation
of humanity's hope for survival.
We must complete it,
at all costs.
And we have to do that
before they arrive.
[SHIMA]
Warp complete.
[AIHARA]
We got it!
The data transmission
from Earth just came in!
Send it off for analysis
at once, and I presume,
that Headquarters is monitoring
the White Comet's
movements, as well.
[AIHARA] Yessir!
You know, at this rate,
we'll be able to talk to them in
real time in about three days.
Deliver all private messages
from friends and family
to the crew now.
Yes, sir.
[AIHARA]
Oh. I can't wait to hear them.
[sighs]
There. It's stabilized.
Captain.
I'd like to go take a look
at the main engine.
[HIJIKATA]
Please do.
Jeez, we're really pushing it.
The daily warp limit is three,
and we've warped five.
Not good.
[OTA]
It's even worse than that.
The Wave Motion Engine's
been infected
with an Anti-Wave Motion
Lattice, too.
[SANADA] Lieutenant Keyman
did cooperate, but still.
Removing it is going to
prove incredibly difficult.
Where is he?
He's back in solitary.
Once the work was done,
he went back on his own.
[KEYMAN groaning]
[groaning]
[TOKO]
Sounds like you're in pain.
Repeated warps are much
harder on the wounded.
You could just go to
the medical room.
But, instead,
you choose to stay.
It's idiotic.
All the same.
I am nothing but a traitor.
If I'm not mistaken, Desler is
the one you betrayed, correct?
[gasps]
[TOKO] Why didn't you
just go along with him?
I know exactly
what Desler is like.
That man has a cold strength,
and an inability to recognize
people as living beings.
Just like you.
That strength gave him
the resolve to kill others,
or even himself, if he
thought it was necessary.
And that's... what I
admire about you--
My mother.
I heard her voice on that day.
[gasps]
[KEYMAN]
When I was rescued,
I hadn't dreamt
about her for years.
But, then...
The one who saved me
wasn't my mother, of course.
It was someone else.
Akira Yamamoto.
Were you disappointed?
No.
[gasps]
For some reason, I was happy.
And I thought, "Is this a bond?
Like those Teresa mentioned?"
[TOKO]
A bond?
That's what she calls the ties
between people, apparently.
Connection. Love.
There are countless
other names for it.
But for the first time,
I think I understand.
I've found it on this ship.
Well, that's very human of you.
To speak so selfishly
and irresponsibly,
when you must know
that love is the source
of humanity's suffering.
[TSUBASA panting]
[MAKOTO]
Tsubasa.
Hey, your dad.
He says his work on the
Yamato is close to being done.
He's coming home!
He can carry you
on his shoulders.
And then, he'll say,
"you've gotten so big" too.
He'll be so surprised.
[MAKOTO cries]
[MAKOTO]
He'll be so surprised.
[MAKOTO sobs]
[KATO]
He's only two years old.
Please let him live!
[baby cries]
[WORKSHOP CHIEF 17A]
Because Noll died in battle
we decided to produce an
emergency clone of Gorland.
[WORKSHOP CHIEF 17A]
In keeping with regulations,
he'll be placed in the care
of the former Gorland.
Zaisen, as you recall.
[ZWORDER]
Why do they smile?
Huh?!
[ZWORDER]
What they do is nothing more
than mechanical labor.
So, what can those people
possibly have to smile about?
[WORKSHOP CHIEF 17A]
Well, who can say?
I have no idea. However...
When they see a recently
produced organism,
for some reason, it makes
some of them smile.
And sometimes, they cry
for no reason, as well.
Well, then, I hear Terezart
is hidden once more.
Also, that Teresa has chosen to
send her Cosmo Wave to Earth.
But, then, if Terezart
has indeed vanished.
All it means is that we are
simply unable to see them
any longer. But Teresa's
still watching.
We will follow through in
our plans to invade Earth.
And to do that...
[GAIREN] We have prepared
a new Silver Priestess.
As was requested.
[GAIREN]
Lady Sabera.
She is not quite like
we Gatlanteans.
Rather, she is a pure
copy of the Zemurians.
Those who created Gatlantis
[ZWORDER] Unlike we clones,
who must be raised from birth,
there is no need to spend
a long time readying her
to fulfill her purpose.
It is all incredibly efficient.
[GAIREN]
To reproduce the body and soul
of a single human
being into a clone--
it still takes a great deal of
memory and equipment.
The Silver Priestess.
This is a luxury that
we could not afford
if she were not the last
remaining human.
"As requested."
That's what you said.
Yes. In addition to the extra
restrictions on her memories--
[ZWORDER]
The suppression of emotion.
There's no issue
with her assimilation
of the limiter system, is there?
[GAIREN]
No, it is perfect.
[ZWORDER]
Like a doll.
[GAIREN] There should be
no lingering resonance
with the Sabera that was
captured by the Yamato.
We've taken care of that now,
as far as we can tell, at least.
[ZWORDER]
No suffering, either.
[BURRELL] For many years,
the Gamilan policy
of expansive colonialism
continued, unchecked.
But with democratization,
our society is undergoing
rapid change.
However, within our country
there are those who would turn
back the clock, and plunge us
into the darkness of austerity
and totalitarianism.
Luckily, we've reports
from the Gamilan police
that today, each of these
traitors has been
indicted and will be punished
to the fullest extent
of the law.
[GIMLEH] Have you any idea
what will befall you
as a result of
taking me prisoner?
You people must not
understand what you do.
The Desler regime is
our only viable future.
[POLICE OFFICER]
Come along quietly.
[GIMLEH] If this continues,
Gamilas will soon meet its end!
[POLICE OFFICER]
Would you shut up?
Averting their eyes from
the bigger picture, I see.
They'll democratize first.
It appears the pathway
for your return to Gamilas
is narrowing rapidly.
However, if you so desire,
we can be of assistance
in restoring you to power.
It seems you have
very few other options.
Thus, I have one condition.
Why, you!
You should already know
that I have no intention
of being a puppet for Gatlantis.
I do.
But you also wish to save
Gamilas from ruin, do you not?
You are a realist and
a reasonable person.
Unlike your nephew.
[gasps]
Just who are you? Really?
My condition is this...
[MIL]
Defeat the Yamato.
[HIJIKATA]
The Transit Wave Motion Gun?
[SANADA] Using the Anti-Wave
Motion Lattice as a Booster,
we'll wrap it around
the Wave Motion Gun.
[SHIMA]
So, since we can't remove it,
you think we should
just burn it off?
[YUKI]
Okay, but what will that do?
It can only be used one time.
But I predict that it will
lead to a rapid increase
in the amount of energy
that's emitted.
Most likely,
it will be exponential.
[GROUP gasps]
[SHIMA]
But isn't that dangerous?
It is. However,
we know the theory,
and we have the equation
at our disposal, too.
We'll tie the Lattice
to the Gun.
The wound caused by
Lieutenant Keyman's betrayal
will ultimately give us
incredible strength.
[gasps] Is this what
Teresa spoke of?
Bonds and their power?
Come on, that seems
way too convenient.
[KODAI]
I agree.
But, at the same time, the
Transit Wave Motion Gun may
be our one ace in the hole for
defeating the White Comet.
Sanada, earlier you started to
explain Zworder's thinking.
In terms of why,
as the Emperor of Gatlantis,
he might want to get
his hands on Teresa.
Well. Keep in mind it's a
hypothesis. For starters,
Teresa's a being who resides
in a higher dimension.
She can see all of time,
from beginning to end.
Therefore, if she were to
fully appear in our universe,
it'd be dangerous.
Our universe could
lose its mutability.
Which means it would petrify.
Huh?
Yeah, so. Uh...
What's that mean?
You don't have to understand
the science, just the result.
That level of interference
from a higher life form
would rock the foundations
of our dimension.
[HIJIKATA] Which would mean
the end of our universe.
[ALL gasp]
Yeah, but we've already met
and spoken with Teresa
at this point.
Nothing bad happened.
[SANADA] That's because we only
got a glimpse into the world
beyond our own through the
window called "Terezarium."
[SAITO sighs]
What is Gatlantis's goal?
The elimination of all life,
and that includes themselves.
That's it. The only
thing Zworder wants.
[DREADNOUGHT CREW 17A] More than
a hundred Karakrum-class ships,
and that number's rising!
Well, then, the time has come.
[COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER] Call
from Enceladus Garrison force!
[YAMANAMI]
Put them through.
[COMMANDER 17A] Greetings. This
is Enceladus Garrison Force.
Fleet command, do you read?
Large number of enemy ships
spotted in orbit of Saturn.
Request immediate reinforcement.
I repeat. Large number of enemy
ships orbiting Saturn. Req--
[COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER]
Transmission lost.
Likely because of
comms interference
from the enemy's warp.
They think they can intimidate
us with their numbers
and break through the center.
It's turning out exactly like
the Ginga's AI predicted.
[AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLER]
Replacement of shipborne planes
with Cosmo Tiger is complete!
We'll stick to the
original plan. All ships!
Prepare to warp!
[ANDROMEDA XO]
All ships, prepare to warp!
[PRESIDENT] As of today,
the Earth Federation
has fully entered into a state
of war with Gatlantis.
I can assure you that,
at the present moment
our forces are greater than
during the war with Gamilas.
There is no doubt in my mind
that they are more than capable
of protecting the
lives, property,
and territory of all
the citizens of Earth.
That is what the Wave Motion
Fleet is for, after all.
We have no other choice but
to rely on their strength now.
[SANADA] With the Transit Wave
Motion Gun, we may be able to
blow away the White Comet's
highly pressurized gas.
[SANADA]
We'll make it in time.
Warping out!
Stick to the protocol!
[DREADNOUGHT CREW 17A]
Nazca-class ships. What is this?
Unknown ship has been spotted!
[COMMANDER 17A]
Bring it up on the main panel.
[DREADNOUGHT CREW gasps]
I didn't even know they could
build ships of that size!
I see. This Must be
their flagship, then.
Flying Corps! Have all
planes dive, now!
Eaters! Prepare to launch!
And deploy catapult attack!
[DREADNOUGHT CREW 17A] Multiple
small battleships just launched
from the carrier! Incoming!
[ESCORT SHIP CREW 17A]
Small battleships incoming!
[ESCORT SHIP CAPTAIN 17A]
Shoot them all down!
The Eighth Ship!
Its Wave Motion Shield
has been breached!
That can't be!
[DREADNOUGHT CREW 17A]
They sank E-23!
How many ships
do we have left?
Eight Escorts, only six Kongos.
[growls]
[DREADNOUGHT CREW 17A]
Multiple Karakrum-class ships
approaching from above!
What?
All The Karakrums
have been destroyed!
[COMMANDER 17A]
Uh? Is it Yamanami?
Do they actually believe they
can win with such meager troops?
Continue pressing forward!
Only a fool puts excessive
confidence in numbers alone.
Wise men recognize that power
will almost always
defeat quantity.
[VALSEY'S XO]
What? Sir Valsey.
New enemies have
suddenly appeared
from the directions of Dagua,
Bomi, and Zemun!
They now have twice
their previous numbers!
[gasps] How could Earth have
acquired a fleet of this size?
Valsey.
I won't tolerate stagnation
of the front line.
I trust you understand
what I mean.
Yes, sir!
[ZWORDER]
Interesting.
Looks like I might enjoy this.
[gasps]
Emperor...
[KATO] Two more warps and
we'll be on the battlefield.
Get everything ready to go, now!
[PILOTS]
Roger!
[KATO exhales]
[beeping]
[KATO] "There is a
way to save your son.
Contact Toko Katsuragi
for details."
Assume the Inferno
Cannon formation!
Hello, and welcome.
To hell.
[ZWORDER]
Now we shall crush them.
[YAMANAMI]
Destroy the Gatlantean base
inside the Comet!
[NANBU]
What is that thing?
[OTA] How are we even
supposed to fight it?
[KEYMAN]
What have you done?
[TOKO] The only thing that
can save a dying child
is a parent's pure love.
[KATO]
Tsubasa.
I'm sorry.