Yay, Falcon!
Here, this is Daddy's!
Thank you, Tsubasa,
but are you sure you want
to give it to Mommy?
No! I changed my mind!
[HARADA laughs]
[HARADA] That's crazy.
The Yamato rebelled?
[KATO] Yeah, and I've been
served a subpoena from
the Bureau of Defense.
[gasps] So did you know?
[KATO]
No.
They think they're
being considerate...
...leaving me on the outside.
[KATO growls, yells]
[KATO] Just me.
I should be there with them.
[YAMANAMI]
This is the flagship Andromeda.
Aldebaran,
Apollo Norm, Achilles,
Antares, and Class D ships,
commence deployment
on both wings.
Launch all fighters!
[YAMANAMI] All ships
to multi-line formation.
[YAMANAMI]
Ten seconds until go.
Eliminate all targets in area.
[YAMANAMI]
All ships, open fire!
[SHINOHARA] I don't know why
I didn't question it before.
How strange it all was--
building an entire fleet of
battleships in just three years.
[YAMAMOTO] The time fault...
You think it really exists?
[SHINOHARA]
I doubt they were joking.
They took off knowing they
were committing treason.
[YAMAMOTO] You're right, and
now there's no turning back.
Yeah. Guess we should
move out, too.
[SERIZAWA] We've received
reports of deserters
from the fleet running
drills around Jupiter.
Mm...
Lose one card and the
house falls to pieces.
We must act now.
We'll secure the Yamato.
Whether by surrender or by fire.
[YAMANAMI]
Pursuit team, launch.
[YAMANAMI] XO, how many
former Yamato pilots
are part of these exercises?
Only the eight that
already deserted, sir.
But there are approximately
30 of their students
flying in the drills as well.
[YAMANAMI]
We can't risk mutiny.
Order all of their students to
this ship, and detain them.
[XO 5A]
Hm?! Sir!
The little rats are
joining the big one.
And we've been called
to hunt them down.
Approaching inner rim
of the asteroid belt now.
I know it's for camouflage,
but isn't this risky
without the Shields up?
Since we're not ready
to warp yet,
it's the best chance we've got.
Sorry it's come to this,
but we're going to need
at least another five hours to
exchange the Wave Motion Coils.
Until we leave our system we're
in the Defense Force's backyard.
So stay sharp,
and watch that radar.
Sir.
Hey, Analyzer.
[ANALYZER]
Yes, sir.
[SANADA] Can you access
Niimi's personal file?
[ANALYZER]
Of course!
Perfect. Try running a word
search for "Izumo Plan."
[HARADA]
It's okay. You should go.
You had a vision, right, Sabu?
Telling you to be on that ship?
That settles it.
Then that's where
you're meant to be.
Makoto.
[HARADA] Tell me,
why do you think she left?
The Yamato.
They came out of nowhere!
Takuma! Your six o'clock! Evade!
[TAKUMA]
Copy that!
Damn it. So much
for a unified Earth.
[HARADA]
I've been thinking about it,
and I feel like I
know the reason.
It's our turn now. That's why.
[KATO]
For what?
When Iscandar offered help,
the whole world was overjoyed,
weren't we? They rescued us.
They heard a voice, crying
out, and they answered.
And this time it has to be us.
That's why the Yamato launched.
Because it's our turn to answer.
[HARADA] During that war
and that journey
we all did whatever we could.
None of us knew how
things would turn out
or if we'd make it back.
And we didn't need to know.
Now we'll do our best again.
That's enough.
That's what matters.
That's all we need to
be able to tell Tsubasa.
Go be the dad he'll be proud of.
Go help for Tsubasa.
For him and for me.
Makoto.
[HARADA]
Go! Board the Yamato.
[SHINOHARA]
What was that?
--[alarm blares]
--[SHINOHARA gasps]
[SHINOHARA]
An EMP attack?
Our ships can't tell
friend from foe now.
Who would want that?
[KEYMAN]
Only machine guns will work.
[gasps] Who's this?!
[KEYMAN] This makes it
all about the pilots.
Of course. If they can't use
their missiles or radar,
then I can crush
them with skill.
[KEYMAN]
That's the spirit.
[YAMAMOTO]
Uh?
A Gamilan?
[BURREL] I realize I've
told you this before,
but Gamilas owes a great
debt to the Yamato.
And now it has left
Earth once again,
on a journey across the stars.
But this time,
the roles are reversed.
Ambassador Burrel.
Earth will take care of this
matter as we see fit.
[BURREL]
I know.
Which is why we feel
compelled to honor our debt.
[YAMANAMI]
We're dealing with a rebellion.
Seems the trip to Iscandar
has affected your crew.
It's made them forget
the real order of things.
[YAMANAMI]
Attention, all crew!
This ship will now
embark on a mission!
Our target of pursuit.
The rebel vessel... Yamato !
[TOKUGAWA] It's a good thing
they never got around
to remodeling this
section of the ship.
[SANADA]
Indeed.
But still. We inherited
all of this equipment
from the old Izumo Plan.
How will it help us now?
[SAIJO] Fighters approaching
from above, starboard side!
They're here.
[SAIJO] We've identified
some of the models.
Space Fighter Attack Plane,
Cosmo Tiger Two.
Hold all fire until
I've given the command.
We won't be the first to shoot.
[SAIJO]
Fifteen seconds to contact.
[gasps]
[CREW gasping]
[SAIJO]
ID codes are a match.
It's... The Lunar Surface
Air Corps! Yamamoto's team!
The Cosmo Tigers.
Open the hatch, bring 'em in.
[CREW laughing, cheering]
[FIGHTER SQUAD
laughing, cheering]
Hey.
[KODAI]
It's been a while, hasn't it?
D'you know anything
about that Gamilan fighter?
[KODAI]
Yeah, it's from the embassy.
[KODAI] Lieutenant Keyman.
Wanna tell me why you're here?
I've already told you.
When I requested to board,
I wish to be an advisor
on this ship.
This voyage will be
full of unknowns.
Our Gamilan knowledge
of Terezart can help.
Why don't you just tell
us what you know?
Let me stay;
you can trust me.
[SHIMA] Heh. You might as well,
Acting Captain.
I mean, we are a little
shorthanded.
Do you mind?
Ship at 12 o'clock! Closing
rapidly at 32 space-knots!
Distance: point-seven
light seconds.
Contact in 130 seconds.
Hey! That's the Andromeda !
How are the Shields?
I'm swapping in
the last coil now.
[AIHARA]
The Andromeda 's hailing us.
Put it up on the main screen.
Have you stopped to think
about what you're doing?
Obeying ghosts of the dead?
Listen to me, Acting Captain.
Turn back your ship.
We can't turn back,
we know something terrible's
about to happen out there.
And what will you do
when you realize
the Yamato can't
handle it alone?
[YAMANAMI]
Think clearly.
First, you need to come
to terms with reality--
The reality is we're heading
toward the wrong future!
Last warning. Turn back.
Your order's refused.
That's a pity.
Quick! Crew to battle stations!
Shima. Set a direct course
for the asteroid belt.
I want you to go in.
Wait, go in?
But the Shields
aren't online yet!
Do it. I have an idea.
[SAIJO] Distance from Andromeda:
point-three light seconds.
[YAMANAMI]
We'll force them to stop.
Prepare to fire graviton spread.
Our target is the Yamato.
Fire!
[SAIJO] The asteroids in front
of us have been obliterated!
Keep your cool.
We're out of range.
Depth charge launchers
standing by!
Fire!
[TOKUGAWA]
Fire magnetron wave.
[SURVEYOR 5A]
Target locked.
Fire!
[XO 5A]
Confirmed hit, all shots.
What is that, sir?
[YAMANAMI]
An asteroid hull.
They dipped into the history
books for that old move.
Almost, Chief!
Can you just buy me
another minute?
Release asteroids!
EM induction to maximum!
High-speed rotation.
Protect the hull!
Spinning now!
[TOKUGAWA]
Asteroid layer depleted to 50%.
Come on! A little longer!
[TOKUGAWA]
Asteroid layer to 30%.
[ENOMOTO] This is Enomoto.
I'm all done down here!
Halt EM induction!
Deploy the Shields!
All energy to the bow!
[SAIJO] Ten seconds until
contact with the Andromeda.
--[KODAI] Brace for impact!
--All crew, brace for impact!
[YAMANAMI] Your boy's
unbelievably stubborn...
...Admiral Okita.
[XO 5A] Captain, permission to
reverse course and pursue.
Uh. Captain?
[COMMS. OFFICER 5A]
Urgent call from HQ.
On screen.
[TODO]
This is Headquarters.
We are Issuing
a fleet-wide order
for all ships in the system.
You are to cease your
pursuit of the Yamato.
[TODO] Suspicions of treason
against the Yamato crew
have been lifted.
Let me repeat.
Suspicions of treason
against the Yamato crew
have been lifted.
Lifted? But why?
I told you that we could help.
You're welcome.
We thank you sincerely,
Mr. President, sir.
I just hope you're happy.
[BURREL] The time fault
doesn't only affect Earth.
The future of Gamilas
depends on it, as well.
If you go after those
who learn it exists--
that sets a dangerous precedent.
There's a nasty rumor
that the leak came
from someone connected
to the Gamilan embassy.
That true?
If it is true that would
be terrible, sir.
We'll launch a thorough inquiry.
[BURREL] In any case,
there are no consequences
for the Yamato 's rebellion.
Your military command
has now sanctioned
their voyage to Terezart
and will give them
operational independence.
Are you sure that's
an acceptable outcome?
[PRESIDENT]
You got what you wanted.
I'll worry about that.
[TODO] Crew of the Yamato,
as Chief Commander,
I will now issue
your official orders.
You will uncover the truth
behind this apparent crisis.
Do what you must, and then
return to Earth safely.
That is all.
[gasps]
[XO 5A] As you ordered, I had
that squadron take it with them.
All their students requested
to transfer to the Yamato.
Did you want them onboard
because you guessed
this would happen?
[YAMANAMI] No, I wanted them
as hostages, as a last resort.
But it all worked out.
[KATO] This is former Yamato Air
Corps Commander Saburo Kato.
Requesting permission to dock.
--[AIHARA] Kato!
--[NANBU] It's Kato!
[OTA]
Kato came!
[KATO] Tsubasa, this is the
Yamato. Daddy's other ship.
[KATO] I want to show you
this one, too.
[TODO] The Yamato could
never face them alone.
[YAMAMOTO]
Isn't it contradictory
to simply watch while
our own people drown?
[KODAISHIMA]
It's too risky!
[KEYMAN] The Yamato as it
is now has a major weakness.
I think you know what I mean.
[KODAI] Begin rescue mission!
We're going to Planet Eleven!