Shirou Emiya, he's looking good.
Isn't he, though?
With Ayako Mitsuzuri and Shinji Matou in the lineup,
we'll win the rookie tournament.
Yeah, we're a shoo-in.
Though, Ms. Fujimura...
compared to the other first-year students,
don't you think Emiya is, well, different?
Sorry. It's hard to put into words.
Getting hurt during your
part-time job before the tournament.
What are you thinking?
Is inconveniencing everyone just something you do now?
I'm sorry.
But, hey, the team has you and Mitsuzuri.
You guys can win easily.
Sorry.
I'm home.
Beginning synchronization.
Tracing basic structure.
Component materials...
tracing.
Altering fundamental structure.
Strengthening component materials.
It's raining.
Hey, wait a sec... Aren't you Shinji's little sister?
That's right.
I'm Sakura, Sakura Matou.
Shirou!
I came by to check up on you!
How's your shoulder? Feeling any better?
This isn't what it looks like!
I promise. It's completely innocent!
Believe it or not?
I've somehow been making do on my own all this time.
And besides,
it'll be terrible if me to make a
friend's little sister pick up my slack.
Well, as Shirou's legal guardian,
I just can't let you do this.
Here, I'll tell you what!
I'll help him with the housework,
so you don't have to worry!
How's that?
You'll never guess who I ran
into while I was out and about!
Next up, we'll be discussing...
The dishes are in the upper cupboard.
The lower one has the rice bin and kitchen knife.
And right down here...
No!
First, fold backward from the back
side around the middle of the shoulder.
Try to fold the sleeves so they're
parallel to the creases in the shirt.
Do the same to the other side,
but be careful so it holds its shape.
Don't worry. This is good for your first time doing it.
I'm going to try it again.
Okay, let's start from the beginning.
Right, then.
If you'll excuse me...
Of course! We'll see you tomorrow!
That's right. I remember now.
A year and a half ago,
I unexpectedly lost against an underclassgirl
who I never thought was that stubborn.
The seasons changed.
But even after my shoulder healed,
that life didn't change.
I can't remember if Sakura insisted on it.
Or was I the one who wished for it?
Either way, it's just a trivial detail now.
If anything changed, it's the fact
that I didn't go to team practice anymore.
I wanted more hours at my part-time job anyway,
and it didn't matter what I did
as long as I could train my body.
So my situation worked out for the best, I guess.
Oh, there's one other thing that
may be trivial in the long run.
Hey, I'm home.
Welcome home, Shirou.
These days, I don't use my keys as often as I used to.
Merry Christmas to the both of you!
As I was saying...
Shirou is cute, truly.
He's imitated Kiritsugu forever.
He wanted to be a hero of justice, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
That booze has gone to your head.
This Kiritsugu,
he's... he was Shirou's father, wasn't he?
He was indeed.
And for Shirou, he was a true hero,
which probably explains why he wanted to be just like him.
You have someone like that in your life, don't you?
A hero of my own...
Shirou.
Emiya. Hey there.
Issei, what's up?
Well, now, great timing, Emiya!
Don't just stand there. Help us out with recruitment.
Hang on. Who's this?
Oh, she's Shinji's sister, and...
Huh? Seriously?
How's it going?
You interested in archery?
I mean, of course you are,
'cause your brother is doing it!
Oh, what's your name?
I'm Sakura.
So you're Sakura!
Well, then, come join the Archery Team!
Unless you've found some other team to join.
No, I haven't.
Perfect then!
She's so pushy. How rude.
...it's a done deal!
Problem, Emiya?
Nuh-uh.
Hey, Shirou!
Thank you for taking our picture, sir.
You realize that you're a teacher, too.
Oh. Um, sorry.
Eh? What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
All right, guys. Big smiles now!
Trace on.
Aw, man.
I'm gonna have to take it apart again.
Sakura, dear!
It's getting close to dinnertime.
Have you thought about what you're going to cook tonight?
I picked up some fresh eggplants today,
so I think I'll make some arrabiata.
Sounds delicious! I'm looking forward to it.
Ah, this scene again.
It's like an old memory being
licked clean by the color of flames.
It's telling me that I'm not
allowed to wallow in my memories.
However, I see the terminus I usually
arrive at whenever I'm dreaming...
a sign that I'm going to be waking up soon.
Shirou?
Fell asleep again?
Good morning, Sakura.
Hey, Sakura, you know you don't have
to come by my place every day, right?
I'm sure you have lots of things of your own to do.
Oh, no, I don't mind, really.
My only hobbies are cooking and archery.
Just so you know,
my goal is to make food that's even tastier than yours.
And I think I'm getting really close to a breakthrough.
Is that a fact?
So your master plan all this
time has been to steal my secrets?
You bet. Prepare for your imminent defeat.
And besides that...
I can't enjoy eating meals,
except for when I get to eat them with you at your place.
Let's go.
We gotta hurry if you're gonna
make it to morning practice.
I've been meaning to ask, Emiya,
are you currently dating Matou's younger sister?
Oh. Well...
I happened to see the two of you coming to
school together as if you were a happy couple.
She's my friend's little sister, man.
Of course we're not dating.
By the way, if you saw us, you
could have said hi or something.
I'm sure you're well aware that I'm still in training.
I don't have the courage for such a thing just yet.
Of course not.
All right, here.
I'm finished with this one.
Good morning, Shinji.
Hey, Emiya, I see you're still
buttin' in like earlier this morning.
One might even say it's your favorite pastime.
I'm not busy, you know.
If you need help with anything, I'm available.
You've never been good at restringing
and mending bows, so we can start there.
You do remember you're no longer with the Archery Team?
Or are you that forgetful?
I think it'd be best for all involved parties
if you simply minded your own business.
We'll begin with pronunciation.
Even if it's spelled the same,
that doesn't mean pronunciation follows suit.
It's easy to slip up, so be careful.
Emiya, aren't we having lunch together?
Sorry. I'm eating in the cafeteria.
Hey, Sakura...
Sakura.
Hi, Shirou.
Hey, wasn't that girl...
Oh, yes.
She's one of the second years.
Tohsaka, wasn't it?
Rin Tohsaka?
I didn't know you knew her.
Uh, she's pretty famous, right?
Always in the middle of the spotlight?
Yes, that's true.
Miss Tohsaka, she's beautiful and awesome, too.
What's wrong?
Tell me, Shirou,
are you planning to quit the Archery Team for good?
It's complicated.
Think Shinji would blow a gasket if I did?
In truth, I think he finds it hard to deal with you.
Then again, I'm positive he
likes you more than the others.
He's not honest with his feelings,
so he's mean to the people he likes sometimes.
That's quite the troublesome personality he has.
Thank you for walking with me.
Insects?
But it's winter.
How weird.
Come now.
I hear you've done a fine job of
taking care of my granddaughter.
Oh, uh, excuse me, sir.
My name is Shirou Emiya.
I'm a classmate of Shinji's.
Emiya.
Is the Einzbern girl in good health these days?
I'm having this dream again.
I remember.
After this, I was saved by Kiritsugu.
If you don't summon yours real soon...
you are going to die...
Big brother.
Next in the news...
late last night, there was a massive gas leak
in a large-scale facility in
the New City district of Fuyuki.
It is believed that the leak originated
in one of the underground restaurants.
Done.
Sakura, grab a plate.
Oh, sure!
Dozens of people who were near the building...
Hey, you okay?
...they, too, feel ill.
Police are investigating whether the
source is a natural occurrence or...
Are you sure you're all right?
You didn't eat a single bite of the breakfast we made.
It's all right to skip practice now and again.
You heard your faculty advisor.
I'm fine. Really, I am.
Um, Shirou...
I have a favor to ask.
Can... Can you come straight home after school today
and get home as soon as possible?
This news just in.
Four residents were found dead in a home early
this morning in the Miyama town district of Fuyuki.
The Fuyuki Police report
that the victims were murdered
by an object akin to a sharp blade.
Emiya.
Emiya!
Morning, Emiya.
Morning, Mitsuzuri.
Emiya, would you happen to know anything
about the murder in Miyama town last night?
Wait. There was a murder?
Were they able to catch the culprit?
No, not yet.
I'll have to have the clubs
cancel their after-school activities.
Excuse me.
Ryudou, do you have a minute?
Yes, of course.
Sorry, Emiya.
We can talk about all this a little later, okay?
What are you doing here, Emiya?
My, my. A first-years classroom.
What could you be up to?
Still here?
I thought practice was cancelled for today.
Practice or not, I keep myself busy
with a plethora of other activities.
Hey, if you're up to it, you can...
Don't be such a pain to Mitsuzuri.
Watch your tone.
An outsider has no right to say that.
I just remembered, Emiya.
There's something I need done, and only you can do it.
'Kay. What is it?
I want you to handle some stupid
cleanup work for the stupid Archery Team.
I don't mind, but it's your job, isn't it?
Didn't you hear me?
I've got more important things to do.
You're not busy.
So I can ask you for help, right...
Emiya?
All right. I'm happy to help.
Fine then.
Why don't you go do what I said, Mr. Nice Guy?
All extracurricular after-school
activities have been cancelled for today.
All faculty students are required
to vacate the campus by 1800 hours.
Come on. Let's head home, sweetie.
Okay.
See you tomorrow!
See you later!
Hey, what do you say we check out that shop?
Sure, I've been dying to go there.
Let's go! Let's go!
I'm so excited!
I guess I must have lost track of time.
I should go home.
The hell...
Who's there?!
What's going on?
What the hell was that?
I gotta get out of here.
If I don't, I'll die.
Hey there.
So pathetic.
All too premature
and, for that matter, all too poor a summon.
We have all the players we need,
but their quality and the precision
of the stage are both lacking.
This Holy Grail War is a far cry from the
grand ritual that we originally sought after.
But we don't have the option of
cancelling something that has already begun.
If the goblet has been filled to the
brim naturally someone must drink it.
Fortunately, the current overseer
from the Church is that man.
I'm confident he will find a way to
mediate this distorted Holy Grail War.
The Grail calls forth Heroic Spirits,
who are in need of Mages to make pacts with.
If the participants are roped into this ritual,
their destinies will be to kill
anyone who stands in their way.
What's important is that only
one needs to be standing in the end.
The seventh Servant who was summoned to
fight in this battle is none other than that Saber.
And its Master happens to be Emiya's son.
How strange fate can be.
The Church is a neutral zone.
No one can meddle with them there.
The question is, will the man turn out
to be a saint worthy of speaking the gospel
or something else entirely?
Is everything all right, Emiya?
For the life of me, I can't fathom why an half-baked
amateur Mage like you was chosen to be a Master.
Whatever the reason, you'll learn about the
Holy Grail War from the guy we're about to meet.
Though, I should warn you he's quite despicable.
You never accepted my invitations to come by,
and now here you are with an odd guest.
I see.
I take it this means that he is the seventh.
I am Kirei Kotomine.
I'm sure Rin told you, but I'm in charge of this Church.
Shirou Emiya, huh?
And I assume that you are Saber's Master. Am I correct?
It's true that Saber has saved my life and protected me.
But if a Master is something a proper Mage becomes,
you would be better off picking someone else.
We should choose a new Master, you say?
How interesting.
In that case, I take it you don't care
about what happened ten years ago, either.
The great Holy Grail
is the omnipotent power in the field of Magecraft,
a granter of wishes that can realize any desire.
In order to obtain this power,
the previous Masters fought a fearsome
battle in which they killed each other.
As a result of this clash,
an accident triggered a deadly event.
You could even call it a catastrophe.
No way.
The big fire?!
Yes, you're right.
Everyone who lives in this city
knows about the losses of that day...
500 casualties, 134 structures burned down.
The blaze that ravaged the city,
whose mysterious origin has been
unknown to the public to this very day,
was the legacy of the last Holy Grail War.
Emiya, what's wrong?
Hey, Kirei,
I only told you to explain the rules to him,
not open up old wounds!
That Holy Grail thing, it's for real?
During the last war,
a man momentarily held the Holy Grail in his hand.
So what happened to him?
Why, nothing at all.
That Holy Grail was not able to achieve completion.
The Grail never lands in the hands of a man
who does all he can to run away from a fight.
Really? You sound like you've
seen the thing with your own eyes.
I did see it...
since I fought for it during the previous war
as one of the seven chosen Masters.
Wait! You never told me that!
I fought until the halfway point,
but I made a wrong decision.
Because of my mistake,
I was only able to hold an empty Holy Grail.
What does that even...
I know we're in the middle of our chat,
but it seems there's an impatient guest outside.
Hey, does the name Einzbern ring any bells?
Now then, young man,
there's no time to waste.
What have you decided to do?
Emiya!
If you're telling me the Holy Grail War
was what caused that disaster ten years ago...
then...
I'll do it.
I'll fight as a Master!
You should be rejoicing.
The wish in your heart will at last come true.
For a hero of justice
must have a powerful villain to defeat.
Well, I guess I shouldn't have
expected a Servant to remember.
So are you all done chatting?
Good evening to you, big brother.
My name is Illya...
Illyasviel von Einzbern.
Thank you for being so courteous.
Okay, I'm gonna kill you now.
Get them, Berserker.
Saber!
Run.
Please, run!
Of all the times for Archer to be hurt.
That's the way, Berserker!
She's got the ability to regenerate her body,
so you can violate her after beheading her!
Damn it. I'm a fool.
Wait!
No way. Why?
This can't happen.
It's no fun.
Master!
Damn it! Why is he so reckless?!
When I was a child,
I looked up to heroes of justice more than anything.
But you can only be a hero for a short time.
Once you become an adult, it's harder to claim to be one.
Kiritsugu.
Besides, choosing to save one person
means deliberately choosing to not save another.
I don't understand.
What do I have to do to become a hero of justice?
What?
I'm healed.
Master...
are you all right?
You're awake, finally.
Tohsaka.
Hold on. Did you heal me?
No, the wounds were healed via your own power, Master.
You're joking, I don't have the
power to do something like this.
If that's true, then perhaps your pact
with Saber had some influence on you.
Not so fast.
You gotta tell us why you acted so recklessly earlier.
Why? What I did back there wasn't that bad, was it?
Actually, I could have done much better...
I think you're missing the point.
We Servants depend on our Masters' magical energy.
If we lose that,
we also lose the ability to remain in this world.
Oh. I didn't realize...
Make sure you don't forget it.
I've got to get going now.
I have to get back to my own
Servant in order to heal his injuries.
Oh, and remember we'll be enemies
the next time we see each other.
Deep down...
she's a really good person.
Saber, how are your wounds holding up?
They're okay,
but not completely healed yet.
Hey, uh, Saber,
do you want the Holy Grail, too?
Yes. It's the reason I'm here in this world.
So about Berserker's Master,
she said her name was Einzbern.
Small kids like her fight in this?
Uh, Saber?
Someone's here, and they're using Magecraft.
But I'm not sensing Berserker.
This entity is different.
Your orders, Master?
Let's go.
Please be careful.
A barrier has been erected.
I know this feeling, but from where?
Mitsuzuri?
Leave her alone!
What a surprise.
To think my curiosity would lead directly to you, Emiya.
What's going on?
I suppose an explanation would be useful.
You could say I had the captain
of our Archery Team lend me a hand.
How could you?
Emiya...
is that your Servant with you?
Since you've shown me yours,
it's only fair that I introduce you to mine.
What do you say we have them duke it out?
I've always wanted to witness a
battle between Servants up close!
What the hell?
Shinji, you're a Master?
Nothing gets past you, does it?
I come from a family of Mages.
The Matous are one of the Three
Great Families of the Grail Wars.
Although, I can't say I wanted an amateur
like you finding out that I'm a Master.
But given my status as the firstborn son...
I think it's only natural that I
participate in the Holy Grail War, right?
Shinji!
You're such a dumb ass, as usual.
But you know how to play this game, don't you?
This is a game of the utmost importance!
And make no mistake, I'm playing for keeps!
Now take her out, Rider!
I, uh...
Hey, who gave you permission to be defeated?
Stand.
Stand up.
On your feet right now!
Do you understand what you're doing?
You're making me look like a loser and weaker than he is!
What?!
Why is this happening?
Damn it, extinguish!
Extinguish! Extinguish! Extingui...
Shinji.
It seems this was too much for you to handle, Shinji.
The Matous have suffered a shameful defeat.
Quite the bitter disappointment.
You again.
Grandfather, please wait.
I am the Mage of the Matou family.
This is my birthright!
You're an incompetent fool who's a failure in every way.
Our bloodline has fallen to its lowest depths.
I no longer have any expectations
as far as you're concerned.
What's that mean?
Hold on! Please come back!
Is Sakura gonna be forced to do something like this, too?!
Why?
Why are you bringing her name into this all of a sudden?
I am the true Mage of the Matou family.
She is a piece of damn trash!
What could she know about Magecraft?!
I was supposed to be the only one in the
family that could receive the Matous' teachings!
Mitsuzuri.
She's a victim of the Holy Grail War.
It's best to ask the overseer for help.
Honestly...
to think you'd return in only a matter of hours.
Fascinating.
You are spellbound by something evil.
I'll take it from here.
You're still here?
How is she?
I finished all of her treatments.
There's no need to worry.
But I must say,
you look to be worse off than she is.
I've already been healed.
In the battle ten years ago, I faced a man much like you.
He insisted on standing before me,
even after suffering fatal wounds.
He was the last man that I fought in the previous war,
and after he claimed victory in our battle,
he went on to win the Holy Grail.
What's more...
his name was Kiritsugu Emiya.
Saber.
Mitsuzuri's gonna make it.
Excellent.
You were in the Church for quite some time.
About that...
we had a talk about Dad.
His name was Kiritsugu.
Master...
It's time. There's something the two of us must discuss.
In a word, I suppose you could sum up
Kiritsugu Emiya as being an assassin.
He was a killer who made his living by
specializing in the assassination of Mages.
It's true that Mages are outlaws who
have strayed from the path of virtue,
but even among them, he was quite an anomaly.
The last time, I was also beckoned to this era,
but I fought as a Servant of the Einzberns.
Then, my Master's name was Kiritsugu Emiya.
That said...
He was truly a man possessing neither blood nor tears.
If it ended in his victory, he would seek out any method.
And once a Master was his target,
not even the ones who begged for their lives were spared.
Out of all the other participants,
Kiritsugu found the priest to be his greatest foe.
He and I...
had a complicated relationship.
I guess you could say that killing
each other was really our only option.
We committed ourselves to the
task of winning the Holy Grail War,
and in the end, we were victorious.
However...
Kiritsugu Emiya did the unthinkable that day
when he betrayed the Holy Grail.
After we had gotten the Grail,
he destroyed it.
He killed one in order to let ten live.
An incorrigible saint,
the likes of which I'd never seen before.
No matter what the priest said,
the Kiritsugu I know
would never dream of abandoning anyone
who'd fallen victim to the Holy Grail War.
He was that kind of hero,
which is why I looked up to him.
So I've decided that I'm going to fight.
I know it's a bit late, but, Saber...
Saber, I want you to fight with me.
No matter what has happened in my past,
this Command Spell now binds me to you, Master.
Yeah.
But would you mind calling me Shirou instead?
Fine. I'll call you Shirou.
Yes, I think I prefer calling you by that name.
Thanks.
So shall we head home?
Yes.
Oh, I see!
You're one of Kiritsugu's old acquaintances.
Still, I'm sorry about your luggage.
I wonder where they could have sent it to.
Hope you don't mind wearing Shirou's hand-me-downs, Saber.
No, I don't mind.
I know that Kiritsugu traveled overseas a lot,
but he never told me anything about his friends.
All right, I want to hear some of your
favorite memories involving Kiritsugu.
Oh, well, let's see.
I know it's sudden.
Sorry, Sakura.
It's fine.
Um, well, anyway, did you...
happen to see Shinji this morning?
Yes, I did. Is there a problem?
No. Just wanted to check in, is all.
Sakura.
U-Um, yes?
Is something wrong?
This bruise, what happened?
Did Shinji do it?
Emiya.
You have some nerve coming to school without your Servant.
What were you thinking?
Listen, if you think so little of me that...
Uh, what are you doing?
I'm begging you, Tohsaka!
Could you give me some advice?
Huh? What?
I see.
Shinji turned out to be a Master,
Ayako got roped in somehow,
and Rider's been taken out of commission.
Well? This can't really be everything, can it?
Also, Shinji has a little sister,
and her name is Sakura.
What is her part in all this?
Not sure...
but she may be dragged into this mess.
I saw Shinji today.
I don't think he's given up on being a Master.
I don't know what to do.
Then how about you keep her safe at your place?
That'd be best,
especially if she's someone who means a great deal to you.
Sakura.
Thank you for breakfast.
It was wonderful.
And you've even gone out of your way to make lunch for me.
I am grateful.
Really? That's nice of you.
That said...
I would like to assist you in any way that I can.
Well, I...
Go! You can do it!
But I...
Um, okay, in that case...
I'm home!
I thought you might need a variety of things.
And here's your luggage.
I mean, they told me it arrived,
so I went and picked it up.
Oh, it's so cute.
Man, I'm gonna owe Tohsaka one favor after another.
Shirou.
I understand that she needs some
daily necessities and things, but
don't you think you bought too much?
Oh, that's right. Fuji-nee...
I think it'd be a good idea to have
Sakura sleep over here for a while.
That's an out-of-the-blue request.
What's going on?
The streets have been dangerous,
and from what I hear, Shinji's been so
busy lately, he hardly goes home anymore.
What do you say?
Well, I...
Oh. Hey, I have a better idea.
You talk,
and I'll get a head start on preparing Saber's room.
I'll go with her.
I see what you're doing.
You don't wanna give Sakura the wrong idea about Saber.
You sly fox.
The wrong idea about what?
Look, you didn't hear this from me, but Sakura has E-cups!
What does that have to do with anything?
Shirou, hurry. It's Sakura.
Shirou?
Forgive me.
These have already come in handy.
Don't worry. I'm not leaving yet.
You're under my guard for another half-hour, so stay put.
Okay.
Then please make sure to watch me, just as you said.
Shirou.
Regarding what we were talking about earlier...
I remember the part about me staying here for a while?
Why'd you ask?
Is it because...
you're worried about me?
Yeah.
I am worried, Sakura.
But if you stay here,
I can always make sure you're okay.
When you put it that way, how could I refuse?
Thanks.
This is the work of something dark and abhorrent.
Soichiro? Is something the matter?
Stay here with the others.
Assassin, show yourself.
Assassin!
Lord Soichiro.
Dear God.
This man...
what is?
First I cut head.
Then arms, legs, I cut.
Belly, I sliced...
but still moved.
You! You're the true Assassin!
Unleash me...
Witch.
There! I did it!
Are you happy now?!
Emiya...
Hey... don't be coy...
Emiya.
Do with me as you like.
Tohsaka.
Shirou...
what are you doing?
Why am I having dreams like that?
Following the mysterious gas leak of the other day,
another gas leak occurred in
the New City district of Fuyuki,
more specifically a building on the
east side of the New City train station.
A security guard and several office
workers were found seriously ill and comatose.
There was damage similar to the previous leak, and...
Saku...
Hello.
Oh, it's you, Fuji-nee.
Right. You can't come today.
Got you.
What?
I went to Ryudou Temple last night.
There was a flow of magical energy
starting at the New City incident,
heading straight to the temple.
Since Archer is back in fighting form,
I thought I would check it out.
Here are my conclusions.
Caster was hiding out in the temple until last night.
By the time I arrived there,
Caster had already been eliminated
by someone else and was gone.
The residents had been stripped of
their magical energy and were comatose.
However, the only one murdered was Mr. Kuzuki.
He was most likely Caster's Master.
Now on to the main subject.
Just this morning,
there was another comatose incident in New City.
Despite Caster already being gone, huh?
Hey, Sakura ended up at your place, didn't she?
Oh, uh, yeah. She started
sleeping there last night actually.
Emiya, let's team up.
What?
This Grail War seems to be totally different
from what my father described to me,
exactly what kind of war we're in this time around.
You're saying you want us to team up for the time being.
Yes, that's what I'm asking.
Rin.
Fighting side by side is meaningless
with a weak Master.
What did you say?
I stated a fact. That's all.
Listen, Archer, as long as I'm
your Master, you'll follow my lead.
Let's get started. Are you available tonight?
You're partnering with Archer's Master?
Yeah. Sorry about how sudden it is.
Don't be.
Thing is...
the faster we finish the Holy Grail War,
the faster Sakura will be able to return to a normal life.
Shirou, I hate to say it,
but maybe she's ill.
No, don't mind me.
I hope it's only my imagination.
Sakura, I heard the bell.
Is someone here?
What's wrong, Emiya?
I am Sakura's big brother.
What's the matter with coming to take
this cute little sister of mine back home?
What kind of big brother hits his sister?!
You roped Mitsuzuri into this.
I can't trust you with Sakura.
Now I see how it is.
You didn't waste time getting handsy with her.
And you can't let go, because you
want to keep getting laid, right?
Bastard!
Shirou!
Shinji.
Well done. That's a good look.
Let's go then.
Time to finish this.
Stop it, big brother!
Sakura.
I'll do anything you ask,
but please don't do this, not in front of Shirou.
Sakura, here's a piece of advice.
Never forget what you just said.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
This isn't something you need to apologize for.
No good. I can't concentrate.
Shirou...
are you in there?
Sakura?
I just...
wanted to talk with you for a little while.
Uh, sure.
First, about earlier,
I'm sorry for what my big brother did to you.
I told you, don't worry about it.
It's cold in here.
Hold on. I'll take care of it.
Come over here.
It's so warm.
You were finally able to fix it.
Yeah.
But I gotta say it took me forever.
Hey, Shirou, do you remember?
Wha?
It's a story from long ago,
so long, in fact,
that it's from before the two of us even met.
It was a bright red sunset.
The courtyard, hallway, and
everything else was bathed in red,
beautiful, yet lonely.
That's when I happened to see someone.
He was high-jumping all alone in the courtyard.
To tell you the truth,
back in those days, I was not a good girl.
As I stood there watching that person,
I couldn't help but think he should just screw up.
But...
He couldn't make the jump, no matter how hard he tried.
In the end, the boy came to realize he couldn't jump,
so he just cleaned up and left.
Hey, Sakura...
are you saying that boy was...
Exactly.
That person was the upperclassmen sitting here now.
You didn't realize it,
but I've known you since way back then.
Surprised?
Uh, I see.
This is the first I've heard of it.
So, um, Shirou...
If you don't mind,
I have a question that may make you uncomfortable.
I was talking to Ms. Fujimura the other day, and well...
she told me that you were adopted into this family.
Yeah. I was.
I was wondering, does it ever bother you that you were?
Not at all.
It took me a while to get used to the idea,
but I never even think about it.
You must feel that way
because everyone around you has always been kind.
Actually, the grown-ups around me were pretty unreliable.
I mean, Kiritsugu couldn't do any housework at all,
and you've seen Fuji-nee.
They were hopeless,
and doing the housework has made me who I am today.
But still, I wanted to be like Kiritsugu.
A hero of justice, right?
Oops.
That's weird. What's wrong with it?
Shirou, I'd like to ask you one more question.
If at some point in the future, I became a bad person,
would you be mad at me?
Yeah. If you did something bad, I'd be furious.
You'd get an earful.
I'm glad.
I'd be fine with that if it was you.
I think I'll head to bed. Have a good night.
Miyama HQ to all paramedics. HQ to all paramedics.
An emergency call has been received from the center.
Civilians are in need of rescue in the
building across from New City Station.
All available vehicles should head that way. Over.
Miyama Paramedic 2 to HQ.
Yo! Was all that commotion your handiwork?
Nah. No way a son of a bitch like
you could pull off such a great stunt.
You won't get away.
Come!
Don't bother.
It's my nature.
Your projectiles are useless.
Protection from stray arrows, huh?
Hiding weapons painted black within the shadows.
Cheap trick.
You saw my face just now, didn't you, Lancer?
Oh, we'll get to that.
Looks like we've reached the end.
But why would a sand bug flee to a watering hole, huh?
You should move, unless you'd prefer to be swallowed.
You idiot. Do you even know what the hell this is?
Damn it.
Noble Phantasm...
Zabaniya!
Damn it!
It's a bit far, but...
Noble Phantasm!
Gae...
Bolg!
Checkmate.
You lose.
Yeah, I've got to admit...
things couldn't have turned out any worse.
Shirou.
Hey, Tohsaka.
Keep walking while we're talking, but,
just so you know, we're being monitored,
so try not to do anything stupid.
Am I right to assume the mayhem was your doing...
elder of Matou?
As expected of Tohsaka's heir.
Your instincts are superbly excellent.
Wait. You're Zouken.
But I thought the Matou had been defeated.
While we may have lost the battle,
I don't seem to recall saying that I'd lost the war.
Archer!
Despicable.
To toy with the corpse of a Heroic Spirit...
how could you?!
No, Saber! Watch out!
Her sword is...
Don't even touch her sword.
The sword probably undoes Magecraft.
It could sever a pact with a Master.
Damn him.
I was going to end this quickly,
but you left me no choice.
As I suspected Caster's Magecraft
won't work on Saber at all.
Although, what if it were used against the Master as well?
What's that?
Impossible!
What is it?
What's going on?
Tohsaka, look there.
It's coming, but what is it?
Imaginary abyss?
It can't be.
It can't be. It can't be!
Shit.
She vanished.
But why?
Watch out!
Emiya!
Shirou!
He didn't touch the body itself,
so it should be nothing more
serious than catching an ague.
Speak honestly.
Do you know exactly what the entity we saw earlier was?
Not quite. But think about it.
That shadow is probably what's stealing
magical energy from the people here.
You're awake.
Are you feeling all right, Emiya?
Y-Yeah.
At this point, I'm in no position to
prioritize my personal grudges anymore.
I'm sorry, Sakura.
I let this happen even though I was with him.
Just leave him with me.
And be quiet.
You're only hurting him further.
So you're here.
Sorry to call for you.
I arrived earlier than expected,
so I decided to grab a bite to eat.
It's fine.
Want a bite?
Like hell!
Get on with it.
What do you want?
Shirou Emiya...
what did you see last night?
You see, I've been observing this Holy
Grail War from the day it first began,
and I received reports from Rin
about the incident at Ryudou Temple.
We engaged Zouken Matou in battle.
He brought Caster to the fight, but it...
it looked like he was controlling a corpse.
So it seems that elder is now on the move.
Listen carefully.
What I am about to tell you
is something not even Rin knows.
The night Caster was killed in Ryudou Temple,
one Servant escaped from its barrier.
Do you understand?
No.
It was Assassin.
How the hell do you know that?
Simple. My Lancer witnessed it.
I just said to you that in this Grail War,
I am a Master.
That means, um...
Damn it. I'm completely confused.
I know what happened,
because I ordered Lancer to monitor Assassin.
He tracked him to Ryudou Temple, but never returned.
Was he defeated by Assassin?
Assassins rely greatly on their
Presence Concealment skills in battle,
but don't have very high combat skills.
Under ordinary circumstances, it
would be impossible for Lancer to lose.
Shirou Emiya...
what you saw last night
was more than just Zouken Matou and Caster, wasn't it?
It's likely that Assassin
was able to lure Lancer directly into a trap.
And whatever's hiding there is not only killing Servants,
but also innocent civilians in the town.
If you liken Caster's ability to draw magical
energy from others to the act of drawing blood,
then what that thing is doing...
is no different than eating.
If we don't do anything to stop it,
the populace will be wiped out.
The number of coma patients has gone up to 30?
The location is Miyama South in Block Four.
Would you happen to know what's in that area?
Ryudou Temple.
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to eat?
You want me to eat a meal with you?
Not gonna happen.
Sakura?
It's starting to snow.
Now then, let me confirm.
Sakura's at your place now, right?
Yeah, she is.
Good. That's reassuring.
This way, I won't have to worry about
her seeing anything that she shouldn't see.
I'm going after Zouken,
so I'm heading there now.
By yourself?
I have a history with the Matou.
It's fine. Leave the battle between archaic Mages to me.
Um, hey, Emiya...
What about you? What's your plan?
Saber...
First off,
I don't have the faintest idea
about what you and Shirou are doing.
I'm sure there are things you
couldn't answer, even if I asked you.
But still,
when you came home last night,
Shirou was terribly injured.
No more.
I don't want him to have to
face that kind of danger again.
I'm... I'm going after that thing we saw.
I can't just let it run wild.
Innocent people here are becoming victims.
I see.
Then we'll keep the truce between us going for now.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I can't let it run loose, either.
That said, don't be reckless.
Until we know more, play it safe.
Right.
Sakura has given me a bitter
pill to swallow about last night.
I admit it was completely my fault
that I was unable to protect you.
Hey, I collapsed because I went off half-cocked.
The problem is my duty is to protect you.
However, I cannot restrain you from joining me in battle.
That said, I will fight with you
and protect you, Shirou.
That is my mission...
and my promise to Sakura.
What the hell?
Shirou!
Sabe...
Shirou, it's Assassin!
You stay there!
Saber!
Like moths to a flame,
you are so predictable.
Zouken...
Matou.
A direct hit by her wind would be fatal.
However...
O wind...
enrage!
Protection Against Wind is a
necessity for those who cross the desert.
Choosing to keep your distance is fine,
but know that your lord is
currently being entertained by mine.
Damn you.
My only objective tonight was to
divert your attention from their meeting.
Damn you, Assassin.
You wretch.
Servants are incapable of opposing that shadow.
Merely touching it will cause one as
pure as yourself to lose your sanity.
But before that...
I will take your heart.
Trace on.
Pathetic.
What can that ruddy old stick do to aid you?
Zabaniya.
Saber!
I'd expect nothing less from the supreme Servant.
She has chosen to confront her own
darkness instead of having her heart taken.
It seems everything has been completed.
Can you tell, young Master?
Can you sense that your Servant
has been annihilated from this world?
Bastard!
I will leave the cleanup to you, Assassin.
You're all right.
How splendid.
Hey, Saber!
Saber!
So you're back.
Start talking.
What are you?!
I see.
There's no denying it.
Officially...
I'm no longer a Master.
What the hell is going on?
These are supposed to be training grounds.
This place...
it's perverse.
Do you hate me?
Do you despise how I tether my
rotting body with the souls of others?
No.
Your obsession for life
is the very thing that makes you fit to be my lord.
There's a black kite.
Milady, a black kite, you said?
Wheep! Takka takka takka!
Sara, get a car ready to go, would you?
Tomorrow morning, I will head out into the city.
I'm not sure who you are.
However, that belongs to the Einzberns.
So have I lost?
What is that?
It can't be.
Don't bother.
That is the Holy Grail!
I must seize it!
In order to do it with my own hands, I must...
I'm telling you,
don't bother with it.
Who's there?!
Do not get in my way!
Who's there, you ask?
That is something...
that should be obvious.
Oh, Shirou.
Where have you been?
Oh, just look at you. You're injured again!
You can't keep this up.
Please take care of yourself!
Sorry.
But hey...
at least I'm home, Sakura.
Yes.
So welcome back home, Shirou.
Hey, Kiritsugu...
I still don't get it.
What in the world do I have to do
in order to become a true hero of justice?
No, I can't end this just yet.
I know who I should fight.
Shirou, you know what?
I thought I'd be able to see you if I
waited here for a while, big brother.
There were two children among the Tohsaka
family who had the potential for Magecraft.
This is the second time I've received something special
from someone who was dear to me.
You'd better die while you still can, girl.
I promise you...
that I'll...