[KANADE]
I'll never lose!
That's impossible!
Justice cannot die!
[TOM]
Always so naive!
There's no justice! It's a lie!
Which one? Who will it be?
Kanade!
I'm done!
Tom! Tom is the winner!
--You're wrong.
--Huh?
The real winner... is love.
[GIN]
Hey, look! A pile of poo!
[TOM] Heck yeah!
That was awesome!
[GIN]
So cool!
Next time,
let's do space robots!
[TOM]
Yeah!
[laughing]
"Love," huh...
[KAHO] Thank you
so much for everything.
[GUARD 7A]
Get home safe, now.
[KAHO]
Yes, sir.
[KAHO] Thank you,
and I'm sorry you had
to come and get me,
Mr. Takahashi.
No, it's okay.
Can you tell me why
you were snooping around
an elementary school, though?
Poor Kaho's in a tough spot.
And she can't
even talk about it.
[CHIAKI]
Ignored by her ex-boyfriend
and mistaken for a stalker?
[SHUGO]
It's complicated, huh?
Oh! I forgot. Someone
called for you from home.
They said you weren't
answering your phone.
It seemed pretty urgent, too.
Yeah, I'd definitely
call that pretty urgent.
You have telegrams, as well.
Who sends telegrams?
Wow, I should probably
give him a call real quick.
[screaming]
[CHIAKI]
Well, that's not disturbing!
[KAHO]
I, um... I need to go home.
[TOM]
Hey, Kanade!
What was your deal
in dodge ball earlier?
You went down
in the first round!
That's not like you at all!
I have something I
would like to add to that.
What is this crap?
You're the best when it comes
to serving fair lunch portions,
but you're way off today, man.
Two carrots?
How could you do that to me?
[GIN]
Are you a pod person?
You guys are right.
Something's off.
I can't say I'm
quite myself, either.
It seems to me that we're
suffering from the same thing.
[KAZ] Kanade, you're
lovesick, aren't you?
I thought he broke up
with that one girl, though!
You mean there
might be a new girl?
--Well, look at the play-ball!
--For real.
[KAZ]
You're thinking "playboy"!
Like Hanako?
[KAZ]
Who is Hanako?
Hey! Are you listening to me?
Who's Hanako?
[KANADE]
Kaho...
Do you get what's going on
with him? Because I sure don't.
Not at all.
But at times like these,
there's only one thing to do!
The Ten Time Quiz!
Yum-yum eat-'em-up,
hooray!
Kanade, say the word
"rest" ten times.
[KANADE]
Rest, rest, rest, rest, rest,
rest, rest, rest...
[NARRATOR]
In the "Ten Time Quiz" game,
one person makes another say
a given word ten times
then asks a question
to provoke an incorrect,
yet amusing response.
It is said to have its
roots in ancient Rome,
where a restaurateur challenged
his customers with "Venus"
and would then jab
them with his elbow
when they inevitably
failed to say "wenus."
Rest and rest.
Nice. Now add a B to it.
So, rest-buh?
[GIN]
No, it's breast!
Say breast!
[TOM]
Are you kidding me?
Kanade just got it wrong!
[laughing]
[KAZ]
Kanade.
[TOM]
What an idiot!
[laughing]
[TOM, GIN]
Rest-buh!
--[KANADE] I'm home.
--[KAZ] Pardon us.
Hey, Kanade.
We're having your
favorite tonight:
batter-fried fishcake
and seaweed.
Aren't you supposed to
gargle when you get home?
Anyone know what's
going on with him?
Maybe. I think he
must be lovesick.
Everyone can tell
something's up.
That's not normal Kanade.
I followed him home
to see if I could help.
But I don't know what to do.
Well, what can you do?
Love is a rough business.
"Children's Telephone Helpline"?
[KAZ] You mean a kid can
simply call this number,
and a grown-up will help them
answer all their questions?
No way! All of them?
That's awesome!
Let's call for help, you guys!
[KAZ] They help you
with your problems?
Kanade!
Don't you have something
you'd like to ask?
What? Me?
Oh! I so know what
I wanna ask a grown-up!
--You do?
--Yep.
[KANADE] Okay, we can
borrow my dad's phone!
[GIN, TOM]
Yeah!
We got 'em!
This might be a good thing.
And they seem like
they're interested.
When you first
mentioned wanting us
to run a children's
telephone hotline,
I wasn't sure what to expect.
I just wanted to
help those boys out.
They're all so worried
about Kanade, you know.
Right, sure you did.
I wonder if that precious Kaz
will call anytime soon.
I've got something
I'd love to ask him!
Love to ask...
What? Aren't the kids
supposed to do the asking?
There's no way
that this ends well.
[phone ringing]
Uh, hello?
Excuse me, sir.
Have I reached the
Children's Helpline?
[ARASHI]
It's Kaz! I wasn't ready!
[screaming]
[KAZ]
Um, are you still there?
Tell me. What kind of
underwear do you have on?
So what happened, Kaz?
I must have dialed
the wrong number.
'Cause I got a pervert.
[KOTA] Arashi, don't tell me
that's what you wanted
to ask him!
[ARASHI]
It was instinct. I'm sorry.
You're the worst!
Those kids are taking
this hotline seriously.
Why can't you?
Next time, I will
answer the phone call!
[phone ringing]
[KOTA] Um, hello,
Children's Telephone Helpline.
I have a question!
Which is softer?
A rest-buh, or a real breast,
or a cream puff?
Ah, boobies.
I want a close encounter.
What? No one cares
about that stuff.
Yuh-huh!
[KAZ]
I agree. That's boring.
[TOM]
How do you know?
Don't tell me you can
already answer that question!
Can you? Have you touched any?
Do you know which one is softer?
Why haven't you answered me?!
[KAZ] No! Look, I...
I don't know! Leave me alone!
Fishy... Normally,
you'd talk more fancy.
No way.
You seriously took the
highway up to Nipple Town?
[KAZ]
No, I didn't take any highways!
I just bumped into them, okay?
Oh, my God.
This is so awkward.
Need to stop this conversation.
Oh, right. Goodbye kids.
[TAGA]
So what happened, Kota?
Huh? Nothing...
He just bumped into them!
Lucky!
I'd love to have a go
at girl-mode Kota's
sweet little peaches!
I could even take pictures
of them from afar.
Play some fun guessing
games like "Pic the Nip!"
[KOTA]
He just bumped into them!
Please quit saying
that kind of stuff.
I'm asking you to stop nicely!
How can you be like this?
What about your girlfriend?
Don't you love Chiaki?
[ARASHI]
Kota.
I love Chiaki more
than anyone in the world.
However...
No matter how
much I may love her,
what I desire...
...will always be
pretty-girl boys.
Nice try.
For a second,
you'd created the illusion
of saying something amazing.
Commonly known as
a classic pervert's trick.
[ARASHI]
You flatter me.
So ask for advice?
[KAZ]
It doesn't have to be.
Just what you're thinking.
What's bothering you.
Putting all that into words
should help you out a lot.
[phone ringing]
Yes, hello?
[KANADE] Is this the Children's
Telephone Helpline?
Yeah, sure, how can I help?
[KANADE]
I, uh...
[TAGA]
Yes, you what?
Don't overthink it.
Just say whatever's
on your mind.
[KANADE]
I thought...
I thought I wasn't lonely
with everyone here.
Go on.
[KANADE]
But I guess I am.
You know, lonely.
And why is that?
[KANADE] I want to talk about
our class killifish laying eggs,
and how the crayfish I
put in the tank ate them all.
I wanna talk about Hanako
who lives in the bathroom,
about how Gin threw up all
the carrots he ate at lunch.
You can tell me about that.
[KANADE]
But I want to tell Kaho.
[TAGA] So you say, but aren't
you the one who ignored her?
I am, yes.
But I didn't know life
without her would be hell!
[TAGA]
What are you saying?
[KANADE]
I just can't...
I can't stand not
being able to see her!
Um, hello?
Look. If you've realized
someone is precious to you,
then you should
really tell them.
I'd let them know before it's
too late if I were you.
I should tell her?
Her, yes! Tell her!
[TAGA]
Kaho's not here anymore, though.
[KANADE]
Why not?
Because she went home.
Could be you'll
never see her again.
[TAGA]
So what's the plan?
If you're okay like this,
let it be over and done.
But I'm not.
[TAGA]
So what's the plan?
[KANADE]
I... I'm gonna go get Kaho!
[CHIAKI]
So you're really going?
I am.
You know she's from Kanazawa
in the Hokuriku region, right?
[ARASHI]
That's a 5-hour trip by car.
[CHIAKI]
And yet...
...you're gonna get
there on a bike?
What's the big deal?
If you have your own bike,
then you can go anywhere!
I'm going, too!
A journey is best measured
in friends instead of miles!
I'm joining.
Where we're headed,
there've been a ton
of UFO sightings!
I'll go and head on home
since Osaka's on the way.
Great timin'!
You're not going
that far by bike!
It's too dangerous
for kids your age.
Besides, Osaka is in
the other direction,
but you're not listening.
Symbolism!
We go fresh! And stinky!
[TOM]
Stinky! Yes!
You need to wear this.
Put it on.
[KANADE]
Thank you!
Okay, see you 'round
and around, propeller!
[GIN, TOM]
Propeller!
[JOJI]
Go!
[CHIAKI]
Where are you going, Taga?
[TAGA]
Why does it matter?
You're so sweet.
[VENDOR 8A] Care for a boxed
lunch, ice cream, beer, coffee?
[KAHO] Excuse me, what kind
of lunches do you have?
[VENDOR 8A]
We have sandwiches and sushi.
Oh, or a seaweed set.
[KAHO]
A seaweed set sounds good.
Wonderful.
Thank you so much!
[KAHO]
Seaweed is Kanade's favorite.
[KANADE]
Kaho. Can I have your seaweed?
[KAHO giggles]
All yours.
[KANADE]
Yeah, seaweed!
I love seaweed! Seaweed!
[KAHO giggling]
Three-second rule!
Boom, and it's safe!
[KANADE]
My wee seaweed buddies!
[KAHO giggling]
[KANADE]
First stage: the straightaway!
All right, you just
leave them straightaways
to the Naniwa Speed Coaster!
[yells]
I tell you what, ain't nobody
fast enough to pass me!
[GIN] Oh, no.
What happened, Speed Coaster?
[JOJI]
I forgot about somethin'.
The one thing that
can cramp my style!
[GIN]
What?
[JOJI]
Red lights hate me!
It's a long one.
"Against the red."
"If we all cross together,
there's nothing to fear!"
[KANADE]
Guys, no!
Kanade, what do you mean "no"?
We're trying to get you
there as fast as we can!
[KANADE] What do you mean,
"what do you mean 'no'?"
Come on! Would you crush the
feelings of the crossing guard
who keeps us safe and will
also say "have a good day"?
Good point, man.
My momma happens
to be a crossing guard.
Wish she wouldn't wear yellow
tiger stripes, though.
You guys, the light
finally changed.
[ALL]
Yeah!
[KANADE]
Second stage: the slope!
I can get up this
monster hill no problem!
[BOYS]
Huff, huff, huff, huff...
Isn't this always the
part where people drop out
because they've
got heat exhaustion?
That's why we
have to have major guts!
[KANADE]
Brother!
[JOJI]
Don't worry about me!
Go! Get the girl!
[KANADE]
I'm sorry, Brother!
Third stage: the mountain!
You ready to cross it?
[GIN]
What for?
[TOM]
A shortcut?
No, we go because it's there!
Awesome! Ha!
[BOYS]
Huff, huff, huff, huff, huff...
Tom!
[yells]
You guys okay?
No!
[GIN]
Keep going!
[TOM]
Dog poop alert!
[KANADE yelling]
[GIN, TOM]
Kanade!
[KANADE yelling]
[JOJI]
It's no use, huh.
[TOM]
What can you do?
We all got flats.
[GIN] Yeah, I gotta get
to cram school anyway.
Kanade, let her go, man.
I won't give up.
I'll never give up!
I'll walk there.
I'll even crawl!
You can't!
[TAGA] If you want to
go that badly, hop on in.
[KANADE]
Taga!
Don't worry about your bike.
I'll take care of it.
[KANADE]
Tom!
And never fear.
I'll get to cram school on time!
[KANADE]
Gin!
Show her your manly spirit!
[KANADE]
See you later!
[KAHO] Home is where
the heart is, right?
[KAHO]
Anyone here?
[MAN crying]
I just got one of
the biggest scoops ever!
According to my big brothers,
if you're going 40 miles
an hour on your bike,
and you do this,
it's supposed to feel
exactly like touching boobies!
--Yeah?
--Cool!
Seriously?
[TOM] Apparently,
it's called "air-petting"!
It's an all-you-can-touch
boobie joyride!
If ya ask me, it's worth a try.
Yeah, but how can
we go that fast?
[ARASHI chuckles]
You can sit back
and let a grown-up
show you how it's done.
[KANADE]
Good luck, Arashi!
[TOM]
You can do it!
[BOYS cheering]
Talk to me, Kaz.
Am I going 40 yet?
Um... Why are you
asking Kaz about that?
[KOTA] Is it because
he's good at numbers?
Not... quite...
I ask... because
Kaz is beautiful!
[moaning]
[ARASHI]
Tell me, Kaz.
Am I there yet?
Oh, yes!
So close! I'm almost there!
I'm there! I'm so there!
[TAGA]
Shut up!
Owie. Taga...
You know you can kick
me more if you want.
You disgusting pathogen.
Great. I'd like to report
a deviant, please.
Yes, and hurry.
[RENREN]
Renren here!
Coming up on
First Love Monster .
[mumbling incoherently]
[RENREN]
All that and more!
Next time: "A Hushed and
Crabby Love Song."
And now, let's
do an impression
of a boiled Echizen crab.
Ready, set, scissors!