[KAHO] Home is where
the heart is, right?
[KAHO]
Anyone here?
Father, are you home? Mother?
[KAHO]
What is that?
[MAN crying]
[DAIKOKU]
Kaho!
Kaho! Kaho!
I'm here.
But why are you?
I didn't know that you'd
come back from America.
Yes.
Well, my project
has stalled somewhat.
But when I arrived,
I was deeply shocked
to learn that my sweet girl
had moved out on her own.
Meanwhile, everyone else--
They've all absconded
to a random villa.
Our home is utterly deserted.
[crying]
Oh, okay.
So that's why you
got in touch with me.
From all the voicemails
and messages you sent,
I thought something
bad had happened.
It worried me, so I came home.
[DAIKOKU] At least
things are resolved now.
Brother and sister have been
delivered to each other again.
And for that, I am overjoyed!
Hey, what's with
all the kokeshi dolls?
Yes. They're adorable,
are they not?
The history of these
dolls has many theories.
My favorite of which is where
kokeshi means child transformed.
When I couldn't
cherish you in person,
I would make a precious
little doll to coo over
as well as distract myself
from my deep loneliness.
Thank you!
This has developed into
one of the best days ever!
I am beaming.
And ever so indebted to you
for returning to me, Kaho.
Now, then.
Tell your big brother why
you deserted this house
to endure life on your own.
Well, I guess it's kind
of complicated to explain.
Oh, yes. Of course.
How terribly sad.
You must have been
sullied and shattered
in that terribly big city.
My darling and delicate Kaho.
No, I'm fine.
I just realized I've been
too dependent on you
and the rest of the family.
I know you were just trying
to protect me, though.
But you can depend on me!
Never fear, for I shall
protect you so hard!
[KAHO giggles]
Well, it's not only that.
I had to learn how to take
personal responsibility.
Blaming my problems on other
people wasn't helping anyone.
I'm sorry.
You should blame me.
For this is entirely my fault.
I left. You needed me.
Yet I was selfishly in America.
I will never forgive myself for
not being here to rescue you.
Don't be silly.
It was a decision that
I needed to make.
You know...
I've kind of been
wondering about something.
Why exactly did you
go to America, anyway?
Mother and Father
said they didn't know
what made you decide
to move there, either.
Oh. I'm doing well,
so never mind about me!
[DAIKOKU]
Now, would you like to watch TV?
I certainly would!
[DAIKOKU]
Does that not sound perfect?
Tonight we shall dine
on none other than
the beautiful Echizen crab!
Oh, sure.
[KAHO giggles]
[KAHO (song)]
♪ Crabby, crabby, crabby. ♪
[KAHO giggles]
This is crazy.
I didn't even know
you had a car.
I don't. It's a rental.
Hold on a second.
Did you rent it for me?
I guess so.
I don't get it.
Why are you so nice?
I mean like, to me.
Probably because I was
right around your age
when I lost my mom.
Seeing you reminds me
of my childhood.
And I can't let you
suffer like I did.
So here I am.
Okay. Well then, why
are you so mean to Kaho?
I dunno.
It's hardly like she's the only
person I'm mean to, though.
My best guess is because
the woman my dad remarried
was like her.
I just generally detest
all wishy-washy women.
[KANADE]
Wishy-washy?
She's not like that.
[DAIKOKU]
Come, you must be hungry.
Dinner is finally ready.
Alas, I had no time to prepare.
I'm afraid this meager meal
is all the chef could offer
last minute.
[KAHO] Our household's
sensibilities are as wonky
as ever.
It looks great!
Thank you for our dinner.
Bon appétit.
[KAHO] Of course there'd
be seasoned seaweed
to remind me of Kanade.
[KAHO]
Hey. What's up?
Can I have your seaweed?
'Kay. Here.
[KANADE]
Thank you!
[DAIKOKU] Was something
not to your liking?
No, it's all great.
[DAIKOKU] Kaho sucked
on these same crab shells
with her own succulent lips.
And this is the pit
from the pickled plum
that Kaho placed in her mouth
and nursed ever so preciously.
Daikoku?
[DAIKOKU]
How did you find your bath?
It was great.
Thanks for letting me go first.
I really needed that.
[DAIKOKU]
Good to hear.
You must be quite exhausted.
I used a futon dryer
to ensure your bed
was as soft and
fluffy as possible.
So, uh... tomorrow...
I'm gonna head back to Tokyo.
To Tokyo? But why?
Oh, please stay a little longer!
You came all this way.
Just make a nice
vacation out of it.
I dunno.
I'd still feel like
I was running away.
Running away?
From what, dear?
Please excuse me.
You were right. I'm more
exhausted than I thought.
Have a good night.
Yes, Kaho.
[KAHO]
Why am I even looking?
Who would message me? No one.
[DAIKOKU]
Kaho seemed off.
What could've happened to her?
I blame Tokyo.
That city is too
creepy for words.
[DAIKOKU] A doting brother
such as myself cannot help
but worry about such
an exquisite creature.
[KAHO]
Good morning, Daikoku!
Good morning.
Hungry? I hope so,
because breakfast is served.
Starting the day with
yet another feast, huh?
Last night, you appeared
rather unwell to me.
So I asked for a special meal.
The chef made snapping-turtle
soup and roasted eel on rice.
[KAHO]
What? I really didn't look well?
[DAIKOKU]
Correct.
You may put on a brave face,
but your brother can tell.
Kaho.
Did something painful
send you back home?
Please tell me.
I'm lost in worry.
Having a good
morning, Kanade?
[KANADE]
Hmph!
You always know.
I can't hide anything from you.
[DAIKOKU] Well, I have
been keeping an eye on
my darling sister for
quite a lengthy time now.
All right, the truth is...
...I fell in love with a boy.
L-Love?
Yes. He's my first love.
And this rogue's in Tokyo?
That dirty city?
What's his occupation?
His pedigree?
I can only assume he must
be quite the smooth customer
to win a heart as pure
and tender as yours!
Um...
Well, actually...
he just dumped me. So...
No! He dumped you?!
I didn't realize this world
contained the kind of villainy
where a man could dump my Kaho!
[doorbell rings]
[KANADE]
Hey, Kaho!
Come out and play!
That voice...
[DAIKOKU growling]
[KANADE]
You there, Kaho?
Come out and play with me!
[TAGA]
You came this far just to play?
[KANADE] What? I don't
know what else to say.
Hey, Kaho!
Come outside and
make up with me!
[gate opens]
[DAIKOKU]
Kaho isn't here right now.
[KANADE]
When is she coming back?
[DAIKOKU]
She's never coming back!
Stop it! What are
you doing, Daikoku?
Hey! Kaho is too here!
Hi, Kanade!
And, hello, Taga.
I don't understand.
Why have you come?
To see you.
And I wanted to let you
know how I really feel.
[DAIKOKU]
Wait one moment!
You lied to me.
Stop getting in the way.
[DAIKOKU]
I beg your pardon?
Daikoku. He's, uh...
[DAIKOKU]
Who do you think you are?
No, you tell me who you are!
[DAIKOKU]
Brother!
Ex-boyfriend!
[DAIKOKU]
Her ex, is it?
I've heard about you!
You're the shiftless
fiend who dumped her!
I shall never forgive you
for such an atrocity!
Kaho, can we maybe
talk somewhere alone?
[DAIKOKU]
I forbid it!
I won't have the two
of you going off alone
into the shadows,
to touch lips or whatnot.
I won't stand for it!
[KANADE]
Like kiss?
We've already done that, buddy.
[DAIKOKU gasps]
[DAIKOKU]
I shan't allow this.
I am her brother, and you
have insulted both of us.
A proper duel is now required!
A duel?
[KANADE]
Red light, green light!
C'mon. Green light!
Red light!
[KANADE]
Okay, fine. Green light.
[DAIKOKU] This confrontation
of the century with Kaho
on the line is
red light, green light?
[KANADE]
Green.
Yeah. You say that, but you're
still going right along with it.
[DAIKOKU]
And just who in blazes are you?
[KANADE]
Red light!
Dang. You guys are
too good at this.
'Kay, I guess it's
green light again!
So, um, that guy is Taga.
The three of us all live
in the same building.
[DAIKOKU]
The same building?
No need to worry.
I have exactly zero interest
in your little sister.
[KANADE]
Red light!
Green light. Keep walking!
[DAIKOKU] I don't know whether
to be relieved or insulted
by your rudeness.
For the record,
Kaho is super cute.
[KANADE]
Green light! Red light!
Green light, green light...
[DAIKOKU]
Tell me something.
Why is the ex-boyfriend
wearing gym clothes?
What is that about?
Is it like a cosplay situation?
Believe it or not,
he's in the fifth grade.
Elementary school style.
[KANADE]
Red light!
[DAIKOKU] There's no way
a person his size
is in fifth grade.
I've had it with
your foolishness.
[TAGA] Why not ask your
sister about her foolishness?
[KANADE]
Red light!
[DAIKOKU] My Kaho's first
love is in elementary school?
He's in the fifth grade?!
How could I allow
this misfortune
to fall upon
my beloved sister?
[KANADE]
Red light!
[DAIKOKU]
I, Daikoku Nikaido,
have made the biggest
mistake in all my 29 years!
Ha, you're out, man!
Kaho's brother totally moved!
Kaho, why were you dating a
child in elementary school?
[KAHO]
I don't have a reason.
I just started liking him.
[DAIKOKU] And you k--
You ki--
You kissed, as well?
[KAHO]
Yeah, but Kanade dumped me,
so none of it really
matters anymore.
[TAGA]
Hey, genius. Here's a question.
Why do you imagine Kanade would
bother to travel all this way?
[KANADE]
Red light!
[KAHO]
Huh? Why he came here?
[KANADE]
Out! I saw Kaho move!
All right!
Taga's the only one left.
Green light.
[TAGA]
Okay, you're cut loose.
Aw. That sucks!
So it's official. I win.
[TAGA]
Since I'm the winner,
I get to keep the idiot
girl as my prize, don't I?
Not so fast!
You don't want her!
You just said you had
zero interest in Kaho.
Yes, that's true, but
I'll take my prize anyway.
Even if it is a consolation
pack of tissues.
[KAHO]
Did he say tissues?
No, Taga.
Refusing to admit
that you've lost?
Doesn't that go against what
your mother taught you, Kanade?
[KAHO]
Taga brought up Kanade's mother.
I wonder what he'll say now.
Yes, it does, but still...
[KAHO]
But still...?
I can't do it.
I won't treat her
like she's property.
And besides, I'm the
one that doesn't want
a world without Kaho.
It was like a hell ruled by
the Dreadlock Lord of Darkness.
[KAHO]
Ooh, Kanade, so close.
But "lock" took it too far.
[KANADE] I just want you
back in my life. For good.
The truth is I love you.
[KAHO]
Oh, Kanade!
Rich words coming from someone
who used Kaho so cruelly!
I can't handle this anymore!
Boy, are you an easy one.
You were dumped and depressed,
but a little "I love you"
gets you all dreamy.
Cheap as bread crusts
that are sold for a dime.
And yet you get so full of
yourself when all the ducks
at the park start
their swarming.
Which is why I'm dying
to keep reminding you
that you're just unwanted waste.
How rude!
If Kaho were bread, she'd
be a fresh-baked baguette!
No. She'd be a fried bun!
But either way,
Kaho is still bread.
[DAIKOKU]
Pardon me?
Your attitude is the very
definition of how one teases
the girl he loves.
Perhaps the truth is that
you really do care for her.
Is he right, Taga?
Is that why you offered
to drive me all the way here?
I see.
I hadn't realized it,
but maybe I like Kaho.
Maybe I bully her
because I love her!
[TAGA] Yes, I must love
this stupid, simple,
wishy-washy, moldy
breadcrumb of a girl.
Unfit to feed the ducks.
[KAHO] Except that's
not something you say
to a girl you love.
Taga's found a whole new game
to torture me, that's all.
I want to hear
what Kaho has to say.
I love you. Forgive me.
Can we please get back together?
[DAIKOKU]
Kaho!
Don't be taken in by his
sweet-talking nonsense!
[KAHO]
I forgive you.
But I can't go back to the way
things were before, Kanade.
A moment, please.
You're not being taken in?
[KAHO] Daikoku. I'd like
to speak with Kanade alone.
[KAHO] Well the truth is
that I do love you, Kanade.
I honestly do.
However...
I'm only a kid,
and still too selfish?
The way it stands now,
we'll just keep repeating
the same things.
And I... I don't
want to be hurt again.
I'm afraid I'll eventually start
to doubt your feelings for me.
Fine. Then I'll do what it
takes to turn into a grown-up
you can trust!
[KAHO] But Kanade, I like
you the way you are now.
There's really no need for
you to grow up in any hurry.
Besides, if you changed,
you wouldn't be the
person I loved anymore.
Then, tell me,
what should I do?
[KAHO]
Do you remember...
That day I met you
for the first time?
[KAHO] Falling for you
made me realize something.
I knew I couldn't stay the same.
I knew I would have to change,
and it turns out that I have.
[KANADE] That doesn't
make any sense, Kaho!
If you like me the way I am,
then I like you how you are.
Let's change together, please!
We'll boost our power!
Don't you want to
special attack with me?
[KAHO]
What is he talking about?
[KANADE] I saw this at an
arts festival in third grade.
The prince and princess,
bound together for eternity.
So you fell in love with me,
an elementary school kid.
What now?
[KAHO]
My heart's pounding so fast,
and I really do love Kanade.
I don't care what anyone says.
I wanna be with him.
Wait... Listen to this.
To Kaho, at 15.
"Love Song to Kaho."
[KAHO]
What is this?
I'm feeling so many
things at once.
Kaho, let's get married!
[RENREN]
Renren here!
Coming up on
First Love Monster .
[mumbling incoherently]
[RENREN]
All that and more!
Next time:
"A Proper Rom-Com for Once."
And now for a match!
Renren, paper, scissors!