[KAHO] I didn't get very
much sleep last night.
[KAHO]
I had my first kiss.
No rest for the wicked, I guess.
You're up!
Morning, Miss Nikaido!
[KAHO squeals]
Good! Yes, I'm up.
Good morning!
The other kids sleep
in when there's no school.
Lucky for you, I made
breakfast anyway.
Eat as much as you like.
Oh, thank you.
[KAHO] I guess that means
Kanade's still sleeping, too.
--Good morning.
--Jeez, Kanade!
You scared me again!
I'm sorry.
But I just can't
take it anymore.
Uh... Take what anymore?
[KAHO]
No. We can't!
This is it. I'm dead!
He'll never find out
if we don't tell him.
[KAHO]
Oh, no! Is he serious?
You don't mind. Do you?
Gimme your seaweed.
All yours.
[KANADE] Yeah, seaweed!
I love seaweed!
[KAHO]
Yup, that's my boyfriend.
He's a fifth grader.
Good grief.
It's too early to be this tired.
[GIN, TOM]
Hello, Jell-o!
I'm sorry to descend on
you in a group like this.
I had planned to
come alone, but then...
We thought it sounded fun!
Provided you boys
don't butt in, it's fine.
Hey, you guys.
Did we have plans
today or something?
[KAZ] Actually, I have
some business with Kaho.
What? With me?
Rather than loitering here,
I think it best if we
repair to Kanade's room.
Wait, why in my room?
It's unbecoming.
Men shouldn't intrude
into the private room
of an unmarried girl.
[KAHO]
Such a gentleman!
[KAHO] I know it's
not much, but here.
[KAHO]
I'm so intimidated.
Feels like I'm dealing
with my mother-in-law.
So you're admitting it, then?!
You serve bad tea!
Why, you're just a demon-in-law!
Argh! I hate you!
I'm sorry, Mother!
Please forgive me!
[KAZ]
You're too modest.
This tea is terribly delicious.
[KAHO]
A sublime gentleman!
[KAZ]
Now, then...
Let me say this once more.
I am very much against
you and Kanade dating.
Allow me to cut
to the chase here.
Tell me what exactly
it is you like about him.
Is it his face? His style?
His immature behavior?
[KAHO]
Well, I...
[KAZ] Perhaps because
he rescued you,
you think he's your
knight in shining armor?
Oh, I know.
You believe fate
put you together.
[KAZ] There is no deeper meaning
to Kanade's words or actions.
Observe.
Enter! Fall into my embrace
and drift back to sleep!
Whoa! It's the
Futonagon monster!
It's gonna try to eat us now!
Think again!
He's a much bigger fool
than you can imagine.
[KAHO]
Unexpectedly persuasive.
In short, you don't
know Kanade well enough
to have feelings for him.
And that's why I'm against
the two of you dating.
[KAZ] Kanade lost his
mother two years ago.
The pain he's
enduring from that loss
has driven him to seek
solace from an older woman.
And you are that older woman.
[KAHO]
What do I say?
He's got a good point.
You know what this
sounds like to me?
Someone is packed
full of bologna!
--Kanade!
--Dude...
She doesn't look like my mom.
That's what bothers you?
[KAZ] All right, so what
do you like about Kaho?
I dunno.
Exactly.
Because you also know nothing
about her. Therefore--
[KANADE]
What's it matter, though?
What does what matter?
[KANADE] You don't fall
in love with someone
because you "know them."
Love is about wanting
to know more,
and then learning more.
That's really sweet.
[KAZ sighs]
Gin, Tom, let's go.
What? We just got here!
I wanted to soak up the
mysterious naughtiness
of being wrapped up
in another family's futon
for a little longer. Gah.
[KAZ] Kaho, I'm still against
you two being together.
Thank you. That was sweet.
I mean it.
No big deal.
But it makes me wonder...
You want to know
more, don't you?
About me?
Oh. Sure.
[KANADE]
All right.
Then come here.
I'll teach you all about me.
[KANADE] I'll show you things
even my father doesn't know.
Show me things even...
and on your bed?
No! Inappropriate! We can't!
I mean, you're in
elementary school,
and beyond that I... you... we--
[KANADE] Secrets and risk
go hand in hand.
That's what growing up
is all about, Kaho.
[KAHO]
So close...
This bad idea just
keeps getting worse!
[KANADE] Just a sec,
I hid it under my pillow.
[KAHO]
Sorry, what?
[KANADE] If I'm gonna
teach you about me,
I figured the best way
would be to show you
what I can do like
super-duper good.
[KAHO]
Oh, yeah.
Look at those math scores.
[KANADE]
Right?
[SHUGO]
Kanade!
How about some snacks
for your friends?
What do you think
you're doing?
Um... This isn't how it looks!
Have you been
hiding these from me?
What do you have
to say for yourself?
Seriously?
Okay, I'm sorry.
[KAHO] Why am I kneeling
down like this, too?
Hiding poor test
scores from me like this
is serious business.
You shouldn't be
hiding anything from me.
Please kill me.
[SHUGO] I'm not going to kill
you over something like this.
I know. I want to take
responsibility, though.
I should own the
mistakes I make.
That's what your
mom always said.
[SHUGO sighs]
I dunno, maybe I'll
just get you a tutor.
No way! That sucks!
I don't want a stupid tutor!
[KAHO] He's pouting.
Like genuinely pouting.
How do you ever expect
to face your mother in heaven
when you've got
grades like this?
[KANADE]
Oh, no!
[exhaling]
I can't snot 'em out! I'm gonna
have a peanut tree in my nose!
Never mind. That was
a close one, though.
[KAHO]
Um, Kanade,
I don't think you're being
very respectful right now!
Sorry. I'll stop.
Well, that was a fast apology.
Nice work there, Kaho.
Seems my son really trusts you.
Duh, of course I trust her.
D'you know who she is?
Hey, you know what?
Miss Nikaido, if it's
all right with you...
[bell chiming]
[GIN, KANADE, TOM]
Ro-sham-bo!
[KANADE]
Royal crown!
[GIN, KANADE, TOM]
Ro-sham-bo!
Shampoo-conditioner, Oh, yeah!
[GIN, KANADE, TOM]
Ro-sham-bo!
Boysenberry bushes!
[NARRATOR] This game is
called Rock-Paper-Sizzle
and Step Roshambo.
Despite regional variation,
the basic phrases
are "royal crown,"
"shampoo conditioner,"
and "boysenberry bushes."
However...
[BOYS]
Go!
Come on!
Stop throwing "ro"!
Otherwise you'll never catch up
with Gin or the winner, me!
Tom's dumb, but you
are doing this wrong.
Find a way to beat your
opponent with just "ro."
For that is the essence
of the game!
[KANADE]
Royal crown...
...and golden throne!
[GIN, TOM]
No... what's he doing?
Well, come and
get me already!
Ha! Points for
hypnotizing us, man!
All right, then,
it's time to initiate Plan B!
[GIN, KANADE, TOM]
Ro-sham-bo!
Boiling wiener attack!
Shamrock naughty place covers!
Soft poop ice cream cone!
[NARRATOR] Changing the
keywords at will during play
can enhance one's
Rock-Paper-Sizzle capability,
pushing them through to a win.
[GIN, KANADE, TOM]
Ro-sham-bo!
Why do boys always
have to be so stupid?
Yeah. I mean, for real, Kaz
could teach them a thing or two.
Um... Right, Yuki?
[KANADE, GIN, TOM]
Tie!
Sure thing, yeah.
Soft-serve poop cream sundae!
[KANADE, GIN, TOM]
Ro-sham-bo!
Awesome. Guess it's a draw.
It's not over! Up for more
after after-class homeroom?
No, I can't.
Dad made me get a tutor.
If I don't go straight home,
my allowance will be docked.
You got to get a tutor?
Dude, that's awesome!
[GIN] Secret, thrilling,
one-on-one lessons.
What's your tutor like?
I dunno.
[KANADE]
I'm home.
[SHUGO]
I know it's a lot to ask,
but would you be Kanade's tutor?
Oh, no! I can't teach.
Sorry, but I'd hate to
make things worse!
What a shame.
It's okay, though.
I'm sure I can find
someone elsewhere.
[KAHO]
I'm a mess.
Although, I do wonder
who his tutor will be...
Wow. Do you even
watch where you walk?
Oh. I'm sorry.
Anyone ever tell you that, uh,
you're like a pile of
dog crap, but worse.
You'll never be
better than that.
So quit trying so damn hard.
[door slams]
What's his problem?
And why does he always
seem to target me?
[TAGA] If I was into anyone
here, it would be Kanade.
[KAHO] Oh, my gosh!
What if Taga's the new tutor?
[TAGA]
That's right, Kanade.
That's how pollination works.
It goes from the
stamen to the pistil.
Taga, I need more than words.
Show me how it works.
So young and
still coming on to me.
All right. I'll demonstrate
so it's easier to understand.
Just relax.
Now, I'll be the stamen,
and you be the pistil.
[KANADE] Whoa!
I'm about to be pollinated!
[KAHO gasps]
What's wrong with my brain?
[MAFUYU]
Ooh, stop it, Kanade! Stop it!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
[squealing]
[MAFUYU]
Oh, no!
Mafuyu, please stop!
I'm tired of studying--
let's play sumo instead!
[MAFUYU] Whoa! Why's it
have to be sumo, though?
[KANADE] Because your
boobs look kinda like
a professional sumo wrestler.
Really? You mean my ladies
are... inspiring?
Guess she's Kanade's tutor.
Mysterious.
[MAFUYU]
You must be Kaho.
Don't worry.
I'm not into Kanade,
even a little bit.
I just want to have his family.
Nice to meet you!
I'm not into Kanade,
even a little bit.
I just want to have his family.
[KAHO sighs]
His family?
She must want to marry him.
[ARASHI]
Well, that was a big sigh.
[KAHO]
Hi, Arashi.
Hey, Kaho. You heading
home from school?
[ARASHI laughs]
I see how it is.
[KAHO] So I think Mafuyu
is into Kanade after all.
And then there's that
whole thing with Taga.
Oh, don't worry.
Listen, Mafuyu's tastes
are a little odd.
They are?
[ARASHI] And as far
as Taga's concerned,
keep in mind his entire
personality is just warped.
[KAHO]
Oh. Okay.
[ARASHI]
We're home!
[SHUGO] Ugh...
They're not in here, either.
We're back.
Is everything all right?
Hey. I'm just a bit perplexed.
It's weird, but I'm coming
up short on dirty laundry.
[ARASHI]
No, not Chiaki's!
Oh, God, no!
Did some pervert steal them?
No, it's not hers, um...
Someone apparently stole mine.
I just can't figure out who'd
take an old guy's undies.
[phone ringing]
[SHUGO] If it's not
one thing, it's another.
[KAHO]
So that's Mafuyu's room.
I sure hope this
doesn't get dramatic.
[MAFUYU squealing]
[KAHO] What the...
What is that sound?
[MAFUYU squealing]
Could she--could she be hurt?
Hello? Are you okay in there?
[KAHO]
She doesn't look okay.
So fruity. So loomy.
[KAHO]
Are those the landlord's...?
Back away slowly...
[floor creaks]
[MAFUYU] I know you've been
standing there looking at me!
[screams]
Nope! Who saw something?
I didn't see anything.
Was there something to see?
Um, Mafuyu,
are you still out there?
[glass breaks]
[MAFUYU]
Hello, Kaho.
[KAHO]
No. No!
Someone, help!
[KOTA]
What's going on out--[gasps]
[CHIAKI]
Why is there screaming?
[growling]
[KAHO screams]
[KOTA]
I'll protect you!
[CHIAKI] She used his face
as a springboard!
[KAHO screams]
[KOTA]
Run away!
[KAHO]
Shinohara, no!
[MAFUYU]
Wait!
[KAHO crying]
[KAHO]
How did I even get here?
[laughing maniacally]
[MAFUYU]
Don't move a muscle!
I have so much to
teach the new girl!
I'm fine! Thank you
for the offer, though!
[MAFUYU] Why, you're
practically quivering, Dearie.
Oh, it's all right.
You don't need
to be afraid of me!
[grunting]
[KAHO]
Surely I'll be okay in here.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[MAFUYU]
I found you.
[screaming]
I swear I won't say anything!
Please don't hurt me!
[MAFUYU laughing]
[ARASHI]
Heads up, Kaho!
[CHIAKI]
Hi-yah!
They're mine!
Almost didn't make it this time.
You're not hurt,
are you, Kaho?
No, I'm fine.
[MAFUYU growling]
[KAHO]
Oh, my God!
She's eating the underwear!
[music playing]
Now calm down, Mafuyu.
That is unless you
haven't had enough.
Done. I ate them all.
Whoo, my tummy's full.
[giggles]
What in the world...?
All right, we're out.
You're on your own now.
[ARASHI]
See you, Mafuyu. Bye, Kaho.
When you saw me before,
what did you think?
[KAHO]
I'm so, so sorry.
I don't want you to apologize.
I want to know what you thought.
What's wrong with
smelling the musk
of someone you love?
Scent synchronicity is science.
It unequivocally proves
that you're compatible
with each other.
It's natural.
And yet another reason Shugo
and I should get married.
Did you say Shugo?
[MAFUYU] I told you, I'm after
Kanade's family, not him.
[KAHO]
You mean you like his father?
Wow.
Um, but isn't he a lot--
like a lot older than you?
[MAFUYU]
Why?
Don't tell me you've got
a problem with that.
You're hardly in any
position to find fault
with someone
else's relationship.
Who's the major perv
that's dating a kid
in elementary school?
[MAFUYU]
Tell me, freak.
What is it about Kanade, anyway?
His face? His body?
C'mon, out with it!
No, it's not about that!
This all started because
Kanade was the first person
to ever get really mad at me.
[MAFUYU]
Who cares, idiot?
How true can that be, anyway?
Since I'm way beyond
mad at you right now,
does that mean
you're falling for me?
[KAHO] Well, I never
said it was logical.
No worries!
Do you mind doing a favor
for me? Your new bestie?
First, this is our secret.
Tell no one, and...
...second, take these
back where they belong.
[KAHO]
My life is so weird right now.
But on the bright side,
at least Mafuyu's not my enemy.
Whatcha smiling about, Kaho?
--Aren't those--
--[KAHO] Kanade?
[KAHO] He's going to think
I'm the one who stole
his dad's underwear!
I swear to you, this isn't,
um, how it looks.
[KANADE] These are the
undies I gave Mafuyu!
[KAHO]
Wait, what?
[KANADE] She asked me for
something that smelled like
the person she loves.
[KAHO] But those are your
father's dirty underwear.
In her own way, she's
making her love active.
When someone has
feelings for another,
you gotta support 'em.
[KAHO] So that's how
Kanade sees things.
It makes sense, though.
He's so innocent.
[KANADE]
Kaho.
Hey. You're flushed.
[KAHO] You're getting
too close, Kanade!
[KANADE]
I know!
Um... What are you doing?
You're clearly tired.
I'm gonna make you feel better.
[KAHO] You don't have to.
It's the thought that counts.
Thoughts alone
aren't good enough.
That's the same thing
as doing nothing at all.
If you don't act on your
feelings, then what's the point?
[KAHO] So, he's acting
on his feelings for me?
He's showing me
how much he cares.
[KOTA]
Oh, no, Miss Nikaido!
You just relax. I got this.
[KAHO]
That feels so nice.
[KANADE]
How about here, Kaho?
Do you like that, too?
[KAHO panting]
[RENREN]
Renren here!
Coming up on
First Love Monster .
[RENREN]
Uh-oh. Not so tight!
I think I'm gonna...!
Oh, no!
[RENREN] All on the next
First Love Monster !
"I Know. To The Bath House!"