Break up? Why?
Because you didn't
hula-hoop enough times?
For real?
[KANADE] The problem is I
couldn't make it over the wall
that I am to myself.
So yeah. I think it would
be best if we break up.
But you were so close.
Only three hula-hoops
away from your goal!
If you rounded up,
that would be 200!
Then would five boobs round up?
[KAHO]
Is this ADD or just a boy thing?
I don't know what he's
picturing, but it can't be good.
[KAHO]
Kanade. I think I feel...
...that I don't wanna break up.
I realize I should
just let this happen,
but I also know how much
I'm starting to love you.
Kaho...
[KOTA]
Kanade, wait!
One more chance!
You gotta believe you
deserve one more chance!
It's not about what I believe.
[KOTA] I get being hard
on yourself and everything.
But what about never giving up?
Don't you think
that's manly, too?
Hey, yeah. Good point.
Kaho, will you give
me one last chance?
Yes, of course I will!
Cool. We can throw
triplefin for it.
[KAHO]
Throw tr--what?
Basically, three rounds
of rock-paper-scissors
decides the winner.
When you throw,
you have to say "triplefin."
Well, you ready, Kaho?
Let's do this.
[KAHO]
What? You're playing me?
Throw on "Go!"
[KANADE, KAHO] Triplefin go!
Triplefin go! Triplefin go!
[KANADE] Kaho... I didn't
know you'd be so good.
[KAHO]
Neither did I.
Why did I have to go
and win three in a row?
[KANADE]
Clearly, this is fate.
What can we do?
Farewell, Kaho.
Ninja out!
[KAHO]
So it's over. Just like that.
Miss Nikaido!
[CHIAKI]
What are you so pouty for?
If you like her, shouldn't
you be happy they broke up?
Why'd you even mention that
"one more chance" crap?
I don't know.
I guess I...
I didn't want to see the person
I like looking so unhappy.
[sighs] Well, if
you think about it,
you did help finish them off
in the lousiest way possible,
so there's that.
[KOTA gasps, whines]
[KAHO]
From the moment we met,
I never knew why, but...
I was attracted to Kanade.
He made my heart pound.
Before long, he was
all I could think about.
He still is.
And when it comes
right down to it,
I honestly can't imagine our
relationship will be different
whether we're
dating or broken up.
In the end, Kanade will
still be there tomorrow.
I don't need to be his
girlfriend right now.
I shouldn't be his girlfriend
right now, either.
If we can't love at the same
speed, I'll wait until we can.
Which is okay.
It's not like anything's
going to change.
[motorcycle noises]
Good mor-ninja!
Your issue of
The Kanade Times!
[KAHO] See, I knew
he'd be the same!
Having a good morning, Kanade?
[KANADE]
Hmph!
You okay?
On second thought, I don't
need any breakfast today.
Now what, pray tell,
made you ignore Kaho?
[KANADE]
Oh, we broke up.
Come on. I'm not that guy.
I can't still be
friends with my exes.
[CHIAKI] Apparently,
someone's been watching
adult-themed television shows.
[KANADE] Once you break up,
the best thing
for both people
involved is distance.
[TAGA] Let me guess.
Your mom told you that?
You do whatever
she told you, huh?
You love your mother. I get it.
But are you sure it's
not an Oedipus thing?
Oh, are you mad at me?
These days everyone gets
angry when you tell them
they have an Oedipus complex.
There's nothing wrong
with loving the person
who gave you life.
So don't make it sound weird.
I don't do whatever she told me.
I just trust she
knew what's best for me
because she loved me, too.
Yes, you're right, of course.
My apologies. I was wrong.
It's cool, man.
[TAGA] It must be lonely not
being able to see your mom.
I'm not lonely.
Everyone else is here.
I can't be lonely.
[TOM] I'll show you
Namiko's upbeat riding style!
Watch this magic!
[NARRATOR] The demanding game
of diving through a hula-hoop
you just threw
requires leg strength
to run alongside the hoop,
incredible balance,
plus flexibility
and decisiveness in order to
jump through it successfully.
Records tell of five princes in
ancient Greece playing this game
to determine who
would take the throne.
It is considered by many to
be the most credible theory
for the origin of the Olympics.
[TOM]
Here, Gin!
Show us whatcha got!
This a dangerous game, though.
Think you can hang?
[GIN]
The more dangerous the game,
the more exciting the hang.
I'll show you that a man
plays the game in ways
that will make
your crotch sting!
What the...?
Instead of going through the
hoop, he just kept running!
No, it's not worth it!
Your wiener, man!
It's gonna hit your wiener!
Ahh...
Whoa! His junk totally survived!
[GIN]
I'm not finished yet.
It just started to backspin!
His butt!
Right between the cheeks!
[GIN]
You're welcome.
I assume you now understand
why I'm always training
my sphincter muscle so hard.
I should have known!
Your wiener and butt
have airtight defenses!
Next up is Kanade.
Allow me.
I don't have
the right to play.
I'll never hula-hoop again.
[GIN]
Aw, man.
So then you, like,
broke up with her twice?
[KANADE]
If only I'd played rock,
we'd still be together!
[TOM]
Hey, chin up, buddy!
There's as many women
as stars in the sky.
At least, that's what
my big brother says.
We get a lot of chicks
in the clinic. Come by!
Wow. Thank you.
You guys are the best!
Cut it out, man.
You're making us blush!
Beep-beep, that is what
friends are for, beep-beep.
[laughing]
[KAHO]
What am I doing here?
This is not what I meant
by "waiting for Kanade."
I can't help it.
I wanna know what's going on.
It's him! It's Kanade.
So are you, like, gonna
head back home right now?
Probably. I'm just
waiting for Tom and Gin.
They're in the bathroom.
Kanade, I heard you broke up
with your dumb girlfriend.
Well, you know those
high-school girls
are basically grandmas.
I'm so glad to be done with her.
Jeez, they're taking forever.
Oh! Yeah, I bet they
had to go poo.
They did have seconds at lunch.
Uh, sure, what with being
growing young-men and all that.
The bottom line, babe?
You're looking at a free agent.
That so? Then maybe I'll
put in my own bid for ya.
[GUARD 7A]
Um, excuse me, Miss?
[KAHO] What do you want?
I'm kinda busy.
"Kinda busy"
doing what, exactly?
Why are you here?
It's not what you think!
I'm not like a deviant! I...
[groans]
Oh! I'm just a simple
high-school girl
who has a crush on an
elementary school boy!
[GUARD 7A] Which means
you're coming with me.
Look, you've got it all wrong!
This is perfectly innocent!
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Sometimes I
randomly hear stuff.
Thanks for waiting,
figure skating!
Pucker up, buttercup,
it's a setup!
[KANADE] All right.
See ya later, Yuki-gator!
[helicopter whirring]
[MAKURAZAKI] May I have
a moment, if you please?
[MAKURAZAKI] I'm terribly
sorry for this disturbance.
Don't be! It's fine.
[KANADE]
Cool, it's Kaz's muttler.
His muttler? Like a pet?
Yeah, he's pretty
much Kaz's pet.
[MAKURAZAKI moaning]
Thank you for
your gracious words!
Master Kanade,
Master Tom, Master Gin.
I, Munemitsu Makurazaki,
need your assistance.
Master Kaz is in
a horrible crisis!
[GIN]
This is the real setup!
[MAKURAZAKI] In the ten years
since I began my service,
a mere 100 days
after his birth...
I have never,
not even once,
seen the young master in
such a state of distress.
[MAKURAZAKI] Unbelievably,
his perfection has been marred.
He has confused his Tuesday
and his Wednesday schedules!
He has failed to arrange
his pencils by length
in their appropriate case.
He even misbuttoned
his shirt whilst dressing.
Kaz did all that?
Doesn't sound like
a big deal to me.
I'm very worried, boys.
His temperature today was 97.2,
so he'll stay home
from school tomorrow.
[KANADE, GIN, TOM]
He's gonna miss school?
[YUKI]
That's a normal temperature.
It would appear my master has...
He's been stricken with
what can only be described
as "lovesickness."
[YUKI]
Huh?
[MAKURAZAKI]
Please, I beg of you!
Do what you can to find
this object of his affection!
And when she is found...
For the young master's sake,
I, Makurazaki,
will do what I must!
It'll be tough,
but we can do it.
We're on the case!
[NARRATOR] Armed with the
knowledge that one truth
prevails... They look like
adults but have the minds
of children. Their names?
The Bamboo Elementary
Young Detective Squad!
And just like that,
the YDS is in business!
You ready for this, Jigen?
Yep!
And you, Goemon?
[recorder plays]
Hey, um...
Aren't they thieves instead
of detectives, though?
All right, now according
to witness testimony...
[KAZ]
It happened not too long ago.
I fell in love with the soulful
owner of this poetry journal.
I couldn't help myself.
Her tears and pure heart poured
on those pages changed me.
--Poetry?
--Pure heart?
It's not them.
Which means Kasumi House
could not have been
the scene of the
love-striking crime.
So where else could
this poetry be going on?
No one writes anything
in gym class, so not there!
Wasn't in the nurse's
office, either.
Well, what about
the bathrooms?
We can't count
those out, can we?
You guys, you're heading
towards inappropriate territory.
Keep in mind, it has to
be a girl we've never met.
I just solved
the whole mystery!
This entire case is history!
Sophestry.
The girl is Bathroom Hanako!
[BOYS]
Yay!
[YUKI] I know I kinda got
swept up in following you here,
but I'm gonna head back.
[KAZ]
I can't believe it.
Hanako? That's her real name?
Swear to me you're sure of it!
Oh, we swear.
Our deductions are flawless,
although she may
be nicknamed "Mary."
Yes, I see.
So the girl I love
is named Hanako.
Okay, what else?
Where does she live?
We hate to tell you this.
She lives in the bathroom!
Bathroom? What?
Our search revealed the truth.
Seems she's in the
bathroom all the time.
[KAZ] There is no way that
a lady would ever live
in a restroom!
She might have a bad stomach.
Most likely, she just
has to poop a lot.
That's an extremely
rude thing to say.
[KANADE]
No, Kaz, it's not.
Women can do anything
men can do, even dookie.
[KAZ] But then, that would
mean my darling Hanako
has been left there to
suffer alone in the bathroom
for who knows how long.
I know! Why don't you
take her some medicine?
As a future OBGYN,
I have to agree with Tom.
But I can't simply
walk into a bathroom
with a lady present.
Not yet. It's far too early.
What are you saying, Kaz?
The woman that you love
is suffering right now!
I couldn't ignore her pain.
Not me.
Kanade?
Hey, guess what?
Kanade broke up
with his girlfriend.
[KAZ] What? You really
ended it with Kaho?
[KANADE]
I did. It's over.
I'm so sorry, I, uh...
[KANADE] However,
it's not over for you yet.
Go give that medicine
to the one you love
with your own two hands!
Kanade...
You're such a wonderful guy.
Come on, Kaz, let's go!
We were prepared.
Her medication is ready.
You guys... thank you.
Sure.
Whatcha snoopin'
around again for?
Fess up.
Me? What?
[TAGA] Just more of
your usual spying crap?
Classic you. A pretty
piece of human trash.
[KOTA]
That's not true!
Kanade came back home really
excited for some reason.
I wanted to make sure
they couldn't involve me.
Right.
You are quite the nice little
toy for those stupid brats.
Hey, who do you think
you're calling a toy?
[KANADE]
Here we go!
[KANADE] The Young Detective
Squad is on the move!
Detectives?
Yeah.
You didn't hear
this from us, got it?
Our sleuth work has
revealed the identity
of Kaz's mysterious lady.
Who's Kaz?
Oh, he's the one of
you that looks normal.
Apparently, it was
love at first sight.
Then, he saw her poetry
journal here yesterday.
Love at first sight, you say?
And we found out her
name is Bathroom Hanako!
As soon as we get the
two of them together,
case closed!
How fascinating.
Okay! You guys ready to head
to the scene of the crime?
[JOJI] No, you ain't
goin' nowhere yet!
[KANADE]
Brother!
[JOJI] You're crazy if you think
you're leavin' me outta this.
Job's one of my specialties!
You know who I am.
Joji Takahashi, elementary
school detective of the west!
Y'mean, you're gonna
join us? Awesome!
Takahashi of the west
and Takahashi of the east
workin' a case together.
Yeah. It's Takahashi
all the way down!
[laughing]
[KANADE]
You crack me up!
[KOTA] Have fun.
I'll just go on back to my room.
[KOTA gasps]
[TAGA] I know you know
something about this.
Huh? No, not me.
I know you know
what'll happen, too,
if you don't tell me.
Okay.
The truth is...
Kaz's mystery girl is, um...
She's me. I was dressed
up as a girl yesterday.
Hey! Why do you look like you
just got some big juicy scoop?
Because I did.
[KANADE]
Infiltration complete.
To the school building!
--[JOJI] Right!
--[TOM] Roger!
[GIN]
Rodger Dodger!
How can a class
president do this?
It's fine.
It's about Hanako, not me.
Why are you
doing this to me?
Those children need
supervision, don't they?
Let's go.
[TAGA]
What's that?
It's Hanako's poetry journal.
I plan to return it
when I see her next.
I've held on to it.
Of course you have.
Well, you never know;
this girl might be a lot closer
than you think.
That's true.
It's funny. I never imagined
we'd be at the same school.
[TOM]
What the heck?
Why's the door locked?
[KOTA] Probably because
it's after hours.
[GIN] You mean like
a locked-room mystery?
[KOTA]
It's not really a room, so...
Anybody there?! Hey!
Did somebody say
somethin' 'bout a locked room?
No crime's perfect with the
elementary school detective
of the west on the case!
[KANADE]
Hold on, Brother!
There's a chance we
might have been way wrong
about this whole thing!
[JOJI] What the heck
are ya talkin' about?
[KANADE]
Isn't it obvious?
How could Hanako have gotten
into the school if it's locked?
[KAZ]
Kanade has a point.
Teachers are the only ones who
should have keys to the school.
[TOM] So what? You're
telling me that Hanako
couldn't even get
into the bathroom?
I feel like this conversation
just took a really strange turn.
Meh, who cares?
No one's getting hurt.
[KANADE] But what if...
What if Hanako could get in
without a key?
What are ya saying, Kanade?
Ya really think
she could be a...?
No, I refuse to believe it.
Nothing about that is
scientific or logical.
There's no way.
I'm surprised you didn't
already know about this, fellas.
Bathroom Hanako
died a long time ago.
She's a ghost.
A ghost?
You can't be serious!
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
I remember something
I have to do.
Not that I'm running
away or anything.
Just spotted the entrance to
the continent of Mu over there.
Well, I'll be.
Y'all are a buncha babies
if you're scared
of a li'l ol' ghost!
Hanako is really a ghost?
Indeed.
Which leads me to believe
that the girl you like
is not actually Bathroom Hanako.
[rustling noise]
[screaming]
[KOTA]
Guys, wait!
Aw, they ran off!
[TAGA laughs] You know,
kids really are the best.
If you were gonna tell
them she was a ghost
the whole time,
then why'd you wait
until we got here to do it?
Hey, who's there?
Turn around!
You can handle this, can't you?
Of course you can't. Let's go.
[KOTA]
Ah! Wait for me!
[GUARD 7A] Hey, you!
Stop right there!
[screaming]
[KAZ]
Oh, Hanako...
You know...
We can't keep meeting
like this, Miss Nikaido.
Who pulls this kind of
nonsense twice in one day?
I'm sorry.
I wish I knew
what made me do it.
[KANADE]
Doo-doo!
Why do you do that?
It's terribly immature.
Nobody should get
that excited about... ahem.
Now, moving on to the
reason we're discussing
this particular topic today.
Many kids can't go number
two in school bathrooms...
Believe it or not,
I get a turn, finally!
Don't worry. We were all
like that when we were kids.
The other way around, Arashi!
Your spoken line and inner
monologue are mixed up!
[laughs] Yeah, I
meant to do that.
Anyway, my point is
that it was pretty rough
for everyone back in the day.
It didn't matter how
popular you were
Once they found out you
dropped a booty bomb at school,
good luck.
You'd be called "pooperman"
until graduation.
That sucks.
So what did you do whenever
you had a frightened turtle?
You just had to hold
it in until you got home.
The worst.
But what if you
couldn't hold it in?
[KOTA whimpering]
If ya don't wanna get
caught makin' butt mud,
ya gotta do it
before anyone sees ya!
The Naniwa Speed Coaster
is a Speed Doodie Doer, too!
Yeah, I don't understand
why it's such a big deal.
Everyone poops.
There's even a book about it.
Amen. Heck, I personally
tell the girls before I'm off
to commit a corn massacre.
Too far, Gin. That was too far.
[ARASHI laughs]
Aw, the good old days
were certainly miserable.
I, personally, never
go to the bathroom.
You don't? How come?
I just don't.
What? Come on, Taga!
Are you like a god?
[RENREN] Coming up
on First Love Monster .
Ken. Ken Tanaka.
Ken Tanaka here.
All that and more.
Next time:
"Kanade's Telephone Helpline."
Sorry, I'm feeling off today.