I just realized...
I bet Kanade doesn't even
think of you as a woman.
[KANADE]
You're gonna catch a cold.
And colds can sometimes turn
into all kinds of bad stuff.
You gotta be more careful.
Kanade...
You can use this
umbrella, if you want.
Oh, but...
I sorta borrowed
it from my school,
so don't lose it.
Thank you.
[KANADE] I've got some business
to attend to, so I'm off.
Business?
[KANADE]
Later, gator!
[CHILDREN chattering]
Oh, wow... This is small.
Of course it is.
It was made for children that
are still in elementary school.
[TAGA]
That's not gonna keep you dry.
Yeah, I know.
What if you caught a cold?
That would be terrible.
Keep in mind I couldn't
care less if a garbage girl
were to catch a cold.
I just know there's a chance
it could spread to me,
and I don't have
the time to get sick.
Gimme that.
I'll give it back
to Kanade for you.
[TAGA]
What's up with him?
Why come home
just to turn around
and go right back to school?
[KANADE]
Sorry 'bout that, Sadako...
Jeez, you got soaked.
I was gonna bring
you an umbrella,
but on the way, I sorta had
to give it to someone else.
Who's there?!
[KANADE]
Taga!
Who's that?
Sadako, was it? Well, well...
You could at least introduce us.
You said you didn't hide
anything from me, didn't you?
Can we please
keep this between us?
I'm begging you.
Don't tell Kaho!
Why not?
Because I don't
think they're ready
to meet each other just yet.
But besides that,
I want to be the one
to explain this to Kaho.
[TAGA]
Understood.
Consider this our little secret.
Do you wanna
pinky swear on it?
It's not just our secret.
The guys know, too.
This is a big deal.
A promise among men...
on our honor.
It appears that you've
gone and grown up, Kanade.
Good for you.
Silly boy.
He sure was in a hurry, huh?
[KAHO]
A paper airplane?
[KAHO] It's an announcement
for Kanade's sports festival.
This is probably a
pretty important paper.
[KAHO]
Is that... Kanade's diary?
I wonder what he'd
even put in there...
Does he actually write
down his feelings?
[KAHO] It doesn't matter
what he writes in there.
Reading his diary
is totally wrong.
[TAGA]
I just realized...
I bet Kanade doesn't even
think of you as a woman.
[KAHO]
But... what if he...
You shouldn't be
doing this, Kaho!
[KAHO] "I want to be
with her every day..."
[KANADE] "...and I want
us to be together forever."
"Every day when I get home,
I'm worried someone
else will take her away.
But I know...
I'm going to have to tell
Kaho about Sadako very soon...
It's my new critical mission."
[KAHO]
What? He what?
Who is this... this Sadako?
[TAGA]
Unbelievable.
Reading your boyfriend's
diary... That's low.
It really is true, then.
You are basic trash.
[sighing]
[CHIAKI] If you keep
on sighing like that,
you're gonna chase
happiness away.
[KAHO]
Too late, Chiaki.
I think happiness has run away
with its tail between its legs.
[CHIAKI] Don't tell me...
It's about Kanade?
[KAHO] Maybe elementary
school kids ought to date
other elementary
school kids after all.
[CHIAKI] What makes you say
that at this stage of the game?
I thought the plan was to wait
and see how he matures.
Yeah, it was,
but that's changed.
I think he might
be cheating on me.
[CHIAKI]
Are you serious?
[KAHO]
Uh-huh.
Looks like it's probably with
some girl named Sadako
at his school.
He likes her.
He wants to share
his snacks with her.
I mean, he even let her
have his favorite jump rope--
the one his mom left him.
And that's not all!
He thinks...
...it feels so good
to hug Sadako
that he never wants
to stop hugging her!
He hopes he gets to
see her in his dreams!
How fascinating...
[KAHO]
In a relationship like ours,
emotional infidelity
is the cruelest kind.
How could it not be?
Our feelings for each
other are all we have.
[CHIAKI] For a supposed
emotional affair,
you sure know a lot of details.
That's because I, um...
I read Kanade's diary.
[MAFUYU] Disgusting!
Reading someone else's diary?
You suck, Kaho!
I know. I'm the worst.
Hey, there.
So, look, Mafuyu...
Thanks for the free show.
[MAFUYU gasps]
But isn't that the
landlord's underwear?
I'd say you suck.
You're the one
wearing stolen skivvies!
Yeah, yeah...
I know. I totally suck.
But still... at least
I don't read diaries.
Diaries contain the
hearts of their owners.
You can peep into a bathroom,
but you can't peep into a heart!
So many things are better!
You can strain your ears
to appropriately eavesdrop,
stand guard while he's bathing,
drink his bathwater
to stay healthy,
sniff the shoes
he's just taken off,
swap your chopsticks for
his when he's not looking,
take his old toothbrush out of
the trash so you can use it,
gather his hair...
[DAIKOKU]
I understand... all too well!
When you love someone too much,
you want everything of theirs.
Like chewed gum as
well as used tissues.
Anything they've
touched is holy.
I don't know about him.
I really don't.
The point is, my dear...
You need not feel bad or guilty
for merely peeking
at that boy's diary.
What child's play!
A diary?
Why, I check your mail
and phone messages,
and I do that every
day without fail!
[KAHO]
Daikoku...
Is that, by chance, my phone?
Wait--you unlocked it?
You're even writing back as me?
Daikoku...
Stop it! Give me back my phone!
[SHUGO]
Kanade!
The sports festival is tomorrow?
Why didn't you tell me
about this earlier?!
Hey! How'd you get
my paper airplane?
[SHUGO] I want you to think
about what you've done.
How many times have
I told you not to fold
important handouts
into paper airplanes?
[KANADE]
I can't hear you!
Well, shoot. Now what?
I've got that trip tomorrow with
the neighborhood association.
[KANADE]
No way!
What am I gonna do about lunch
for the sports festival, then?
I hate this!
I'll be so hungry
after all those games,
but no food for me!
Aw, man... Boo.
[SHUGO] It might be
difficult so last minute,
but I'll see if I can
get out of the trip.
I could just make
you a boxed lunch,
but you'd still have to eat
it all by yourself, poor guy.
It's fine. Go on your trip.
Besides, this is my fault.
[KAHO]
Um... If you want...
I could maybe go--
I can go with him.
[SHUGO]
Taga?!
For real?! You'd do that?
I always end up
going to watch anyway.
We all do.
Gotta cheer you on, right?
[SHUGO]
On your day off, no less!
[KOTA]
And every year,
I somehow get roped
into participating.
[KAHO]
Yeah, I can see that.
Kaho, are you coming, too?
Don't be silly.
Of course I am!
[KANADE]
Awesome!
[KAHO]
Will you please move?
[TAGA]
Boy, you have got some nerve.
Especially considering
you read that diary.
Yeah. Well, excuse me.
[TAGA chuckles]
Now... as for
tomorrow's festival...
See you there, garbage girl.
[ANNOUNCER 11A] It's time to
kick off Bamboo Primary School's
annual sports festival!
[CROWD clapping]
[ARASHI] Yes! There are
so many cuties here!
But where are
Kanade and his friends?
Um... I think I found 'em.
Well, no chance we'll
ever lose sight of that crew.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
Begin the warm-up exercises.
And remember, children,
give yourselves plenty of room!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
[yells]
Gotcha, man!
[CHIAKI]
Oh, they stand out.
But whether that's
for better or for worse...
Yeah, no comment.
Ah! I'm gonna take
some of the best shots today!
[ANNOUNCER 11A] Next up
is the fifth-grade ball-toss.
--[ARASHI] Ball-toss!
--[whistle blows]
[CHIAKI]
Is that fair?
It doesn't seem fair.
[MAFUYU] Wow, they're
literally head and shoulders
above the rest, aren't they?
[LEIA]
Hey, boys!
Don't be selfish.
You need to give all us
girls a chance to play, too!
Yeah... for real!
Why for when we're the
ones used to holding balls?
Unless... that is...
...you're just like super-duper
in love with balls.
Ew, gross!
You guys are
seriously the worst!
[GIN]
You throw like a girl.
--Oh, yeah?
--Take this!
--And this!
--Jerks!
Class! Don't fight!
Come on, guys...
[whistle blows]
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
And the winner of this event...
...the white team!
[cheering]
[drums playing]
Red team, go!
Red team, fight!
Go get 'em, go! Go! Go!
Yeah! Give 'em
that fightin' spirit!
[ANNOUNCER 11A] Next up:
the fifth-grade tug-of-war.
[whistle blows]
All right... bear down!
Okay!
But don't bear down
so hard you poop your pants!
Poopity poop! Poopity poo poo!
Ew! Poop our pants! As if!
Let's get louder, guys!
Heave... and ho!
[GIRLS]
Okay! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
How do you tell
a prostitute to go?
[BOYS] Leave, ho!
Leave, ho! Leave, ho!
Yes, bear down!
Bear down! Come, on ladies!
For your future childbirth!
Bear down!
Shut up, creepo!
Boys are nasty.
Totally nasty.
Yeah.
[GIRLS]
We're done bearing down, boys.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
The winner is... the white team!
Hey, if the red team
loses today,
it's gonna be the boys' fault!
[YUKI]
Kanade... Your knee...
Is it hurt?
My knee?
Nah, I just scraped it a little.
I'm in charge of the first aid.
I can get you a
bandage if you want.
Um... it'll only take a sec.
[KANADE] Don't worry. A little
spit'll heal it right up.
[KAHO]
Of course.
That must be Sadako.
Heh. A high-schooler
who's jealous of
a little fifth grade girl...
Are we shooting for
beyond pathetic, now?
Look. I didn't ask
for your opinion.
And you aren't guilty, sir?
After all, you sound
rather jealous
of that strange Kanade kid.
You think I'm jealous?
I think I'm insulted.
[KOTA] Now, now,
let's calm down, guys...
[DAIKOKU, TAGA]
Shut up, Kota!
Why is it always only me?
[ANNOUNCER 11A] It is now time
for the parent guardian
scavenger hunt.
Those of you who are in
the parent guardian seats...
Let me guess...
I'm the one doing
the scavenger hunt?
[TAGA] Of course it's you.
Who else would it be?
Oh, God...
Why me, though? I'm so slow!
Why do you think we
decided to bring you along
in the first place?
I don't want to!
Last year, I was the worst
at the bread-eating contest,
and then Tom said
it should've been lead.
Oh, just get over there.
Out of all the virgins,
you're my slave.
Now obey me.
Ooh!
So we're both slaves?
Sounds way fun!
[CHIAKI]
So wrong.
[KOTA whimpering]
[ANNOUNCER 11A] All right,
parents and guardians.
Take your place for this
year's scavenger race!
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
On your marks... get set...
[KOTA panting]
[KOTA]
Down to the last card? Already?
And it's in a sealed envelope!
[KOTA]
What the crap?
This isn't a scavenger hunt;
it's a costume race!
[GANG MEMBER 11A]
Come back here, lady!
I've got to hurry!
But, jeez, why women's clothes?
Li'l Renren!
That's right! Gimme the
blah ba dee ba boo stuff!
Um... Arashi?
Do you have any women's--um...
What do you prefer?
Western? Japanese? Chinese?
But it's not lunchtime yet!
[ARASHI]
Li'l... Renren!
[KOTA]
Western, please.
Changing made me so late!
[KOTA gasps]
Hanako! It's you!
[KOTA] I'm so sorry.
I'm in a hurry!
Wait... Please, Hanako wait!
Hanako!
Yo, Kaz.
They been lookin' for
ya back over thataway.
'Kay.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
Ladies and gentlemen,
that brings our parent
guardian scavenger hunt
to a close.
[KAHO]
Oh, you did great!
[TAGA] Except for coming
in last place again.
It's okay.
I took some great photos
and posted them online.
[KOTA whimpering]
[KANADE]
Kaho!
I'm about to
get first place!
[KAHO]
I believe it! Good luck!
Thank you.
Know what time
it'll be when I win?
Smooch time.
Kanade, hush! Not so loud!
[KANADE]
Is that a no?
Well, um... no,
not really, but...
[KANADE]
Well, if you say no,
then I'll really want to do it.
So I'm getting that
smooch either way!
[KAHO] I'd be mad
if he wasn't right...
[ANNOUNCER 11A] Now, the
fifth-grade footrace will begin.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
On your marks... get set...
[gunshot]
[KAHO]
Kanade's so talented. So cool!
Goal!
[KAHO] That was so fast I
didn't get to take a picture!
[KANADE]
Yeah!
What's up?
I saw her. I saw Hanako earlier.
[TOM]
Seriously?!
I don't know where
she went, though.
Maybe that means
I'll see her again.
[ANNOUNCER 11A] And with that,
we've come to the end
of the students' morning events.
While everyone is
eating their lunches,
please pay attention
to the main stage
for a small but delightful...
Wow! It's Li'l Renren,
right in the flesh! Ohh!
[CROWD cheers]
Master Kaz,
it's poor manners
to leave one's seat
unnecessarily during mealtime.
[KAZ]
Yeah, I know that!
Hi, everyone!
Are your lunches tasty today?
[ARASHI]
Yes! So tasty!
Do you know what would
make me, Renren, so happy?
If you were all
eating seafood today!
That's why I've traveled
all this way to show you
the Renren dance live!
See if you can learn it, too,
and feel free to
dance and sing along!
Okay, start the music, please!
[music playing]
[ARASHI]
Woo!
[ALL]
Time to eat!
[KANADE]
Seaweed, seaweed...
[KOTA] Oh, nice!
We got crab croquettes!
Crab cro--croquettes...
[TAGA]
Eat the fried chicken.
[KAHO]
Is Kanade going to kiss me,
or did he already forget?
Oh, no, I bet he's worried
about what that Sadako girl
would think if she saw us.
[KAHO] Diary or not, I still
don't know how he really feels.
Oh, right! I totally forgot!
Kaho!
Come here for a second.
[KAHO]
Okay.
I know.
If I get the chance
to talk to Kanade alone,
I have to apologize for
snooping and reading his diary!
And... I probably ought
to ask him about Sadako
to find out what's
going on with them.
[KAHO]
Uh, hey, so um, Kanade...
I need to tell you something.
I sorta read your diary.
I've been wanting to
apologize for it all day!
I'm so, so sorry!
You read it? For real?
[KAHO]
Yes.
So, who's Sadako? Tell me.
[KANADE]
The truth?
[KAHO gasps]
Kaho...
Just... close your eyes.
[KAHO]
What's going on?
I've never seen him
act like this before...
Surely, he's not gonna
try to blow this over
with a little kiss.
Because that is so not
going to work, like at all.
[KAHO]
And yet... I...
[screaming]
Look, it's Kaho!
Say hi! This is Sadako!
[SADAKO yapping]
You mean... Sadako's a dog?
[KANADE] Yep! I'm surprised
her human face
didn't confuse you more!
She's dangerous, so I wanted
to get her more used to me
before I introduced
her to you, at least.
She kinda gets all worked
up when she's hungry.
[KAHO] So it turns out the
other girl was just a dog.
I got all worked
up over nothing.
Oh, you silly Kaho!
What happened?
We heard this crazy screaming
sound from over here!
Did you see a ghost?!
[SADAKO screaming]
What's wrong?
Kanade, are you all right?
Come here.
You look a little pale.
[KANADE]
Don't touch me!
[KAHO]
Why? What's going on?
[KANADE]
I... I just...
I can't be... I can't
be with you anymore.
What do you mean?
[RENREN] Renren here! Coming
up on First Love Monster .
[mumbling incoherently]
[RENREN]
All that and more!
Next time:
"Adorable/Abnormable."
And now for a match!
Renren, paper, scissors!