[KAHO]
Wait.
Do you mind, um...
Do you mind telling
me your name?
Yeah, I do mind.
I'm not supposed to
give my name to strangers.
Plus, you're kinda creepy.
[KAHO]
And thus my first love ended.
Let me go back
to when it all started--
all the way back
to three hours ago.
My name is Kaho Nikaido.
My family, well,
they're kind of a big deal.
Basically, they're rich.
Like, super rich rich.
My parents treated me
like their little princess.
You could say they
spoiled me rotten.
It's probably because they
had me when they were older.
My teachers and people in town
were intimidated by my family,
so they made sure to
never get upset with me.
My friends were all schoolmates
that my parents asked
to hang out with me.
So as a result,
I have no idea what it's like
to have someone mad at me.
What would you think
of a person like that?
A total disaster, right?
A big loser.
I wish I was never born.
[KAHO] So this spring,
I left my hometown.
And I decided to start
high school in the city.
I guess this is Kasumi house.
Ah...
[KAHO screams]
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to scream--
[KOTA] Excuse me,
are you Miss Nikaido?
[KAHO]
You know my name?
Are you the landlord?
Well... I wouldn't say that...
[KAHO]
He's so young!
Are all Tokyo
landlords like that?
I bet he made a bunch
of money in IT or something.
Yeah, it has to be IT.
And now, he's managing
apartments he bought
--with all that money!
--No, wait a sec!
I'm just a normal
high school student!
The landlord had
other stuff to do today,
so he asked me
to help him out.
[KAHO] Well, I guess that
was a pointless delusion.
Thank you very much.
It's nice to meet you.
[KOTA] Yeah, same here.
Nice to meet you, too.
Can we bring in your things,
or you just gonna keep that up?
[KOTA]
Right. Uh, second floor, please!
[KAHO]
Oh, I don't mind helping!
[KAHO] Wow, these are heavier
than I thought they'd be.
Whoa! Are you all right?
[WORKERS laughing]
Just stay there, little girl.
We don't need you getting hurt.
[WORKERS laughing]
[KAHO]
And here I am in the way again.
No! The kokeshi
my brother gave me!
Wait, kokeshi !
My brother will kill me
if I lose you!
[horn blares]
Do you wanna die or somethin'?!
Didn't anyone ever
tell you not to jump out
into the middle of
the street like that?
If a truck hit a little
bitty thing like you,
you would've been squashed flat
just like an ant or a frog
or a turtle gets squashed!
Hello? Are you even listening?
What is it you want from me?
Just tell me what it is. Money?
A favor from my mom and dad?
I'm not interested in money or
your parents or anything else.
[KAHO]
Liar.
You wouldn't bother
saving a loser like me
if you weren't after something.
[KANADE] Aren't you
supposed to save people
who are about to die?
And I heard if you call
yourself a loser too much,
you'll actually
wind up becoming one.
You're small.
But you are pretty cute.
Come on.
You're a loser, my foot.
[KAHO]
Cute?
Did I hear him right?
[KANADE]
Later.
[KAHO]
Wait.
Um... Do you...
Do you mind telling me
what your name is, please?
[KANADE]
Huh?
Yeah. I do mind.
I'm not supposed to
give my name to strangers.
Plus, you're kind of creepy.
[KAHO] And that brings us
back to where we started.
[KOTA]
Um, are you okay?
Oh, good. I mean...
We wouldn't want you getting
hurt on your first day here.
[KAHO gasps]
He saw that? Oh my god!
The guy I just met totally saw
me fall in love at first sight,
get called creepy,
and then be rejected!
[KOTA] You should know
something about that boy
you were talking to.
[CHIAKI]
Hold on, Shinohara!
[KOTA]
Chiaki!
Let me cut to the
chase here, sweetheart.
Be honest. You fell in love
with that boy, didn't you?
[KOTA gasps]
[KAHO]
Wait, how did you know?
Are... are you a psychic?
No, but people like me
do have a way of just
knowing these things.
[KAHO] You mean like
city high-school girls?
Oh, it doesn't matter anyway.
I don't even know
what his name is.
And it's not like I'll
ever see him again.
[CHIAKI]
What if you did, though?
If... I saw him again?
Like I was trying to say...
Shut it, Shinohara!
Those who'd try and
thwart a young girl's love
should go trip over a kokeshi !
Jeez, no wonder
you're still a virgin.
Hey, that has nothing
to do with anything!
[TAGA] All this racket
outside our front door
is disturbing the neighbors.
[CHIAKI] Taga's being cocky.
What a surprise.
Now, tell me...
Why don't you act your age?
Like you're one
to talk, old man.
Calm down!
Please don't fight,
you guys, please!
Cram it, ya virgin.
[KOTA] It's the super-sadist
versus the brute!
Wait! Why would you
assume I hadn't--
Are you saying I'm wrong?
Ouch, virgin.
You got busted yet again.
Look, I'll have you know--
[KAHO] Have a nice day.
I'm going to my room.
Wait!
[KAHO] I wonder if they're
like that all the time.
I hope I can get used to it.
[KAHO]
So much happened today.
If a guy who saves my life
can turn around and reject me,
I bet no one else will
want me as long as I live.
[KANADE] I heard if you call
yourself a loser too much,
you'll actually wind up
becoming one.
You're small,
but you are pretty cute.
Come on.
You're a loser, my foot.
[KAHO]
No way I'll ever see him again.
I mean, if I do,
that has to be fate, right?
It's you.
Hey, what's up?
I didn't know you lived here.
I do!
Huh...
Good to see ya!
[KAHO]
It's fate!
Wait! Wait up!
Today you saved me,
and I got yelled at for the
first time ever, like ever!
[KANADE]
Really?
Weird. My whole life
is being yelled at.
And... to be... to be honest...
I didn't think we'd
ever meet again.
That makes no sense.
We live in the same house.
It's bound to happen.
[KAHO]
That's true. Um...
Oh yeah, my name is
Kanade Takahashi.
So it's okay to
tell me your name now?
For sure. You can't be a gross
stranger if you're living here.
Okay, it's your turn.
When someone says
what their name is,
it's polite to tell
them yours in return.
You're right. I'm sorry.
It's Kaho Nikaido.
Cool. Later, Kaho.
No, please wait a sec!
Why? What else could
you have to say?
[KAHO]
I...
Um, it looks like...
This is so sudden,
but I think I love you!
[KANADE]
I don't mind dating you.
If you still say you
love me after you find out
who I really am,
then yeah, we can totally date.
Think about it
until tomorrow, okay?
No way!
[KAHO] What did he mean
by "who he really is"?
Maybe he's married?
Or has kids?
What if he's into guys?
What if he's really a girl?
It could be tons of debt.
He could be an alien!
Or from the future!
Does he have ESP?
[KAHO]
I didn't sleep a wink.
It doesn't matter to me
what his secret is, though.
I'll deal with it.
And then...
I guess I'll go out with him.
I can't believe you came!
Tell me.
Well, I'm still
in elementary school.
So what now?
[KAHO]
And thus,
the monster known
as "first love"
began its vicious
assault on my heart.
[KANADE] So are we gonna
go out now, or what?
Oh. I, um... uh...
Okay!
[KANADE]
Cool!
Then starting today,
you're my girlfriend.
[KAHO]
"Cool." Right.
He's the "cool" boyfriend
I've always wanted.
Sorta.
[KAHO]
This is how I die!
What am I doing?
I can't date a kid his age!
Yodel-ay-hee-hoo, Kanade!
Are these your friends?
Yep. We're all
in the same class.
Four eyes over here is Gin.
And this other guy with
the weird hair is Tom.
[KAHO] Do all elementary school
kids look like that nowadays?
Guys, I'd like you
to meet my girlfriend.
Um... Nice to meet you?
Man!
I was gonna be the one
to get a girlfriend first!
She's even older than us!
Good for you.
Be proud.
You're climbing stairs
to adulthood.
[KAHO]
Stairs to adulthood?
[KANADE]
Bye, Kaho!
I'll see you later!
[KAHO]
'Kay! Have a good day!
[KANADE]
And we're off!
[TOM]
And we're awful!
[GIN]
And we're awfully awesome!
[CHIAKI] Well, congratulations
to the new couple.
[KAHO]
No, I was just being nice.
I can't go out with Kanade.
Of course not.
We're talking about a
fifth grader here, girl.
Indecent much?
Criminal? Maybe.
Perverted? Yeah.
But then again,
on the other hand...
You did tell him you'd
be his girlfriend,
so I wonder how he'd feel
if you told him "never mind"
and that you were just
"trying to be nice."
Kanade's a lonely kid.
Although, who wouldn't be
after losing their mother
in the third grade?
[PRINCIPAL] What I'd like the
students of Bamboo Primary
to remember today is "sushi."
Not the food, but the letters.
S is for stranger danger...
Ow, I sprained my fingers!
[PRINCIPAL]
The next S...
Principal, sir, the boys
are acting dumb again!
Yeah.
[KAHO] Even on my
first day at a new school,
I couldn't stop
thinking about Kanade.
Do you wanna die or somethin'?!
[KAHO]
Oh, what am I gonna do?
It's Kanade.
Hey, Kanade!
Why are you running?
[KANADE]
Kaho!
It's Gin!
His wiener is in a bad place!
[KANADE]
Gin! I heard about your wiener.
Wiener pain, go away!
Wiener! Go away!
Shut up!
You can't wish his
wiener away like that!
I mean, get real.
Where's it gonna go?
Huh... into the sky maybe?
Hey, Kaho.
Do you know where
his wiener would go?
My, where would his wiener go?
Yes, where indeed...
You don't think it could
be buried somewhere, do ya?
[KANADE]
I bet it could.
[laughing]
[TOM]
Gin's wiener!
[KANADE]
His wiener's golden poop!
Stop saying that!
It's not my wiener!
Oh, good. I'm happy
everything worked out.
I'll just be on
my way home now.
[KANADE]
Kaho, wait!
You can't go home. You should
play tip-top tag with us.
I don't know what
those words mean...
[NARRATOR 1A] "Tip-top tag"
is a popular game
in elementary schools.
It can only be played when
participants have an opportunity
to get to higher ground in order
to avoid the player deemed "it."
More commonly known
as "high tag,"
it's also referred to
as "climb tag," "air tag,"
and "up-and-up."
Viewers at home, what do
you prefer to call this game?
Woo!
Woohoo!
Two, three, four, five, go!
[GIN]
So close!
Kaho! He's gonna tag you!
Run away!
What? Oh, okay!
[KAHO shrieks]
You all right, Kaho?
[KAHO]
I'm good. I'm so sorry, Taga!
[TAGA] That Kanade's a
rambunctious one.
Try to be careful.
[KAHO]
Right. I will.
Wait up, Taga!
It's good to see you, Kaho!
Kaho! Tom is "it" now, so focus!
You gotta get to
high ground! Hurry!
[KAHO]
Oh. Right.
[TOM]
Snot!
Are you really climbing
those dumb poles again?
[KANADE] Of course he is.
Gin really likes those things!
If you weren't such
a dumb-butt-head,
you might be able to
understand what it is
I like about 'em.
[TOM]
Okay, fine.
What's so great
about stupid poles?
[TOM]
Oh, yeah.
I think I get it.
[GIN]
You're welcome.
Hey guys, whaddaya
think's taking Kaz so long?
Kaz?
[TOM] He's only the most
awesome kid in the whole school.
[GIN] Yeah, he's even
more awesome than we are.
[KAHO] Ah! You mean there's
another fifth-grade boy
who's decidedly
un-fifth-grade-like?
[KAZ]
Oh, yeah.
I'm in elementary school, too.
What of it?
Kaho, don't you go
cheating on me with him.
I would never
cheat on someone.
Well, sure, you say that now.
Watch out.
He might steal her away, Kanade.
He's a big deal.
We're talking about
our class rep.
[KANADE]
Are you trying to piss me off?
[KAZ]
Apologies for being late.
[TOM]
You finally made it!
[KAHO] I wonder if I could
just not turn around.
Let me introduce you.
Kaho, this is Kaz.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kazuo Noguchi.
[KAHO] Finally, a
normal-looking fifth grader!
[GIN] Kaz's awesomeness
made her collapse.
[KANADE]
I know.
I'm sorry if I
disappointed you, Kaho.
Oh, no.
To be honest with you,
I'm kind of relieved.
[GIN]
Whoa.
This feels like a setup
for a girlfriend swap.
Yeah, it does.
What are you gonna do, man?
[KANADE]
Hey, shut up.
I'm not gonna
share my girlfriend.
Kanade, um...
It's embarrassing when
you say it out loud like that.
[KANADE]
Ready?
Back to the game!
[TOM]
All right! I'm still "it"!
Hey, wait a second!
No way. No time-outs!
[GIN]
But it's an emergency!
Ew! Are we timing out so
you can adjust your junk?
Gotcha. No one
wants a wiener leaner.
Wiener leaner?
You get one when you don't
find the most comfortable spot
to place your wiener.
[shrieks]
[KAHO]
Wow...
I've just connected some
extremely mortifying dots!
Yeah, but you can do it
from your pockets, like this.
The direct approach
is more reliable.
Fine, but don't touch
me with your wiener hands!
[GIN]
Heh.
Telling me not to touch you just
makes me want to touch you more.
No! He's got the wiener hands!
Look out!
Gin's got the wiener touch!
[TOM]
Run away!
If you catch it, your fingers
will turn into wieners!
No! Don't you even
think about it, Gin.
You can't touch me
with those things!
[GIN] All I heard was
"Touch me with those things."
Wiener! Wiener!
[KANADE]
Olé!
[GIN]
Wiener.
[growling]
[GIN]
Ding-a-ling!
--[KAHO yelps]
--[KANADE] Kaho!
[KAHO]
He saved me again.
If you see that
a girl is in trouble,
you should always
reach out to help her.
See, my mom taught me that.
Your mother did?
Don't worry.
Trust me.
I'll protect you
no matter what happens.
[KAHO]
Thank you, Kanade.
[RADIO] Attention all
children playing outside...
Oh, crap!
I'm gonna get Namiko's
fists if I'm late again!
[GIN]
I have cram school.
[KANADE]
See you guys later!
[KAZ]
Kaho?
[TOM] Yeah, you don't want to
end up with wieners for fingers.
I should let you know.
It's nothing personal, but I'm
against you and Kanade dating.
[laughing]
[KANADE]
You guys are so stupid.
[KAZ] All right, it's time for
our after-class homeroom.
--[KANADE, KOTA, TOM] Okay!
--[GIN] Bring it!
Today I'd like to discuss the
results you see on this board!
Wow.
You sure did give us
a lot of marks, huh?
Cool.
I've got the second
highest number.
[GIN] And if I have the most,
that means I win, right?
Oh, I know!
That must be the number of good
stuff we've done for the day!
Wrong! It's the opposite!
The more marks,
the more you must reflect
on what you've done!
[GIN]
Wait, what?
It's a tally.
These are how many times
certain words have been said.
You mean like
th-the kinds of things
you can't say like
on TV and stuff?
Those words?
Yes. Precisely those.
For real? What could we have
possibly said that many times?
Yeah, I can't think
of anything that bad.
All we really did today was
hang out on the jungle gym
hitting our--[toot]
and then we climbed the poles
to rub on our--[toot]
I mean, we did take a little
time for [toot] adjusting,
but we didn't say
anything bad. Huh?
[GIN]
The count's gone up!
How come?
[TOM]
What gives?
All he said was
[toot] and [toot]!
There's nothing wrong with that!
Those are normal words!
That's dumb!
[KOTA]
So much noise. Please stop.
[recorder blowing]
[KAZ]
Enough already!
Stop it! I want you to
stop saying "wiener"!
You let them
get to you, buddy.
[KAZ]
Oh.
[RENREN]
Renren here!
High-school freshman Kaho is
dating fifth-grader Kanade.
It's her first love, not to
mention her first boyfriend,
and she's determined
to learn more about him.
All on the next First Love
Monster: "Ah, Kasumi House"!
And now for a match!
Renren, paper, scissors!