Hold on! Not there!
Please, not right there!
Come on, Kaho, I know you
can feel how hard this is.
[gasps]
[KANADE]
Just relax!
[KOTA] Oh, God, what are
they doing in there?
Surely not...
Oh, God, what are
they doing in there?!
you doing out here?
[KOTA] What? Me?
What? Nothing!
I'm not... Nothing!
[KANADE]
You like it, Kaho?
What about here?
Does that feel good, too?
[KOTA]
Chiaki, wait!
Knock, knock! What's going on?
[KANADE]
A massage!
[KAHO sighs]
[KOTA]
Huh?
[KANADE]
Kaho looked tired.
My mom did this a lot
for me when I was tired.
Disappointed a bit there,
Obscene-ohara?
This was all way more wholesome
than whatever you were hoping
for while you were listening in.
Thanks, Kanade.
That was amazing!
Yeah, you still look
real tired, though.
Meaning... it's time
for my ultimate weapon!
We're gonna go to
the super bathhouse!
[KAHO] I can see why this
is a super bathhouse.
[KAHO] I hope Kanade doesn't
look as good in swim trunks
as I bet he will.
[WOMAN 5A laughs]
Don't you do it!
I've never seen men and
women bathe together before.
Really? First time at
a place like this, huh?
--Guilty!
--[KANADE] Kaho!
[KAHO] Kanade's going all out.
And in more ways than one.
[KANADE]
Okay, Kaho.
What bath do you
wanna try first?
Nope, hold it.
This is a bath, not a pool.
So take those goggles off!
And the rest
of you children,
you gone to the bathroom?
If you haven't gone,
then go now!
We don't need you
warming up the water!
I didn't have to
go until you said that.
I wonder how come.
Because you're a
poopy-faced poop-man!
Hilarious.
Fifth grade boys sure
do like poop, am I right?
[KANADE]
Wrong!
See? I'm mature for my age,
so I don't like all
that poop stuff.
And I'd never mistake
poop for chocolate!
Like never ever ever, whatever.
[KAHO]
Oh, Kanade.
No one would say
something like that
unless it had actually happened.
[KAZ]
Kanade.
That's enough.
Off to the restroom. Let's go.
[KANADE, GIN, TOM]
Aww...
[KAZ]
Shut up! Move it, guys.
[KANADE, GIN, TOM]
Fine.
[KOTA]
Uh... Miss Nikaido...
I'm really sorry,
for, you know...
Tagging along with you two.
B-Because I'm, uh,
barging in on your
date, and stuff.
[KAHO]
Oh, right.
I guess that technically
this is a date.
[KOTA gasps]
[CHIAKI] You are such a
masochist, you know that?
[KAHO]
Oh, Kanade.
Wow! My junk won't
move in these!
Awesome!
I've been taking big,
giant steps, too,
and my wiener hasn't budged!
Talk about some
powerful trunks!
Yes. But what if
I did a cartwheel?
Nothing moved.
Beans and wiener are good!
Yeah. Junk security achieved!
[laughing]
[KAHO]
Wow!
They have so many
different kinds of baths!
[CHIAKI] That's why elementary
school kids like it so much.
Speaking of, they
sure are taking a while.
I imagine they're
playing some stupid game.
I should probably
go check on them.
[KAHO]
This was Kanade's idea,
so I feel like I should spend
some of the time with him.
[KANADE]
Bare butt.
[TOM]
Bare buttocks.
[GIN]
Bare behind!
Butt plus butt makes
double-butt buds.
Poo hole! Ooh!
[KANADE] You're not supposed
to do it for real,
but Tom did!
[KAHO] Oh, Kanade,
where did you run off to?
[KAHO yells]
[KAHO]
Is that Kanade?
You're not supposed to run
around like that here.
Didn't your folks teach
ya right, Little Missy?
Uh... okay.
I wasn't running, but, um,
thank you for catching me.
Tell me, darlin'.
What's your name?
[KAHO]
Oh, I'm Kaho Nikaido.
I think I'm in love!
--[KAHO] You what?!
--That's a jolt of electricity!
Bet this is what
fate feels like.
[KANADE]
Stop! Who are you?
[KAHO]
Kanade!
Get your damn hands off her.
That's my girlfriend!
[KAHO]
He's so brave!
It's you!
So you gonna
bring it, or what?
'Cause it's being
brought over here!
There comes a time
in a man's life
where he must fight
for his honor.
[JOJI] I just knew
I recognized that voice.
Howdy, Kanade!
It's me!
Come on, now! D'ya forget?
The Naniwa Speed Coaster:
It's Joji Takahashi!
[KANADE]
Ah! Hey, Brother!
[KAHO] What does he
mean by brother?
[JOJI] When'd you decide
to go and get so big?
[KANADE laughs]
I'm having a growth
spurt, that's all!
Been there, Brother.
Been there!
[KAHO]
A "growth spurt" is all?
That's gotta be the biggest
understatement of the year.
Karma. Reincarnation.
Long-lost brothers,
reunited at last!
It was guided
by the cosmos!
A question, Kanade!
I've known you
since kindergarten,
but this is the first I've
heard of any brother!
Who exactly is that guy?
Wait. You mean me?
[KAHO] So he's not his
older brother after all?
Well, then, who is he?
And what's with that accent?
I'm not his brother.
I'm actually his cousin.
The name's Joji Takahashi.
--Ta-da!
--But you can just call me Joji,
the Naniwa Speed Coaster!
I'm Tom, Brother!
And I'm Gin!
Kaho, darlin'.
Yes, what?
[KAHO]
Darling?
I don't think anyone's ever
called me that before!
[JOJI] Kanade's nice,
but he's still a kid.
I mean, he's in fifth grade!
What are ya datin' him for?
You should date me instead.
[KAHO]
What? No, wait. I, um...
I'm lots more grown up, darlin'!
That's... not the point.
The truth is that I love him!
[JOJI]
So? Who cares 'bout that?
Joji, do you, uh, mind if
I ask how old you are?
I'm in sixth grade.
[KAHO]
Yeah, I figured as much.
It also says so right there.
Oh, good, we found Kanade.
Jeez, are there
more of them, now?
She's my girlfriend. Stop that.
I don't want to have
to say it again, Brother!
Well, I'll be.
It's one woman and two men.
You know what that means, right?
[KANADE]
Say what?
Say who?
Say where?
Say why me?
It's time for battle!
[KANADE]
You ready for this, Brother?
Ready!
Whoever gets the other's
swim cap first is the winner!
Hey, Arashi, this has nothing
to do with us two, so...
...why are we horses?
I dunno. Just figured it was
the path of least resistance.
Let's do this, fellas!
[yelling]
Maybe I should stop this.
[KAZ]
No, leave them alone.
[KAHO] What the--that seems a
little elegant for a bathhouse.
Yes, sir, as you wish.
[KAHO] Are you kidding me?
He has a butler?
Believe me. In my experience,
when you hang out with fools,
you get caught in the crossfire.
Yeah, well, in my experience,
when you hang out with fools,
you should just pretend
you don't know them.
Tom! Gin! Make a right turn!
[KAHO] Kanade seems
so much more excited
now that he's seeing Joji.
For I guess the
first time in a while.
This should be fun!
It's about to get real now!
Here comes my killer move,
the head grab!
Success, boys!
I'm holding the prize!
What? No, you're not!
Whose swim trucks are those?
They're not mine.
They're his!
They're Kota Shinohara's trunks!
No pants! No pants!
No-pants Kota!
Bare butt! Bare butt!
[whistle blowing]
What is this?
Are you guys in high school?
[KANADE]
No way, dude.
Okay, so you're in college.
Either way, quit fooling around.
You all should be
ashamed of yourselves.
You're too old and
grown up for this crap.
We are not too old or
grown up for this crap!
Ah!
[KOTA, ARASHI]
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry...
[apologizing]
So, why are you here, Brother?
You're a really long
way from home.
I'm a traveler, now, man.
I've forsaken my land.
Huh?
[JOJI]
Truth is, Mom betrayed me.
She went and tossed out
all of my Pachimon cards.
[ALL gasp]
No, how could she?
[KANADE] I... I didn't
even know that was a thing.
[TOM] Mothers are fearsome
creatures who can,
on occasion,
perform such atrocities
without the batting
of a single eye.
[JOJI gasps]
My brothers!
That's Kanade's cousin for you--
a man of discriminating taste!
That's Kanade's pals for ya!
Let's take a bath, guys!
Indeed. It shall be a sign
of our reconciliation.
Yeah!
So does this mean
they've made up now?
[KANADE]
Kaho!
Hey, Kaho! Come over here!
Oh... okay!
[laughing]
This is so nice.
Barista, the usual, please.
Chomolungma, sir?
Mount Everest, duh!
[KANADE]
Kilimanjaro!
The Kilimanjaro jar, yo!
[laughing]
Jar, yo! Jar, yo!
[CHIAKI]
It's starting to get dark out,
so you kids be careful.
Thanks, but we're fine.
Makurazaki's on it.
Kanade! Bye-bye-banana!
[KANADE]
Banana-nana buttface!
Whoa!
[GIN, TOM]
Made you look!
[laughing]
[KANADE]
Aw, dang it!
[laughing]
[KANADE] The dinosaur
bath really did it for me.
What about you?
[KAHO]
Let's see...
The diet cola
bath was different.
D'you feel a little better now?
[KAHO]
Mm-hmm!
Kanade. Kaho, darlin'.
May I have a word
with y'all in private?
Um, we're spying on them.
Are you sure that's all right?
Of course!
You should always
prioritize good drama.
Yeah, and besides,
since when does an inveterate
eavesdropper care?
So what's this
all about, Brother?
[JOJI] Remember how I said I
came here because my mom
threw out all my Pachimon cards?
--Sure do.
--[JOJI] Well...
Ha!
The whole truth is that I
been holdin' this ultra-rare
3S card on my person
the whole time!
What? No way!
That's the "Gaia
Whispers 'Shine'" card,
and it's gorgeous!
Ew! Did he just pull that
out of his underwear?
[JOJI] I been holdin'
it this whole time!
[KANADE]
No way! It's gorgeous!
[TAGA] What are you guys
spying on this time?
[KOTA]
Oh! Hi, Taga!
Shh!
[JOJI]
I'd like it to be yours.
Seriously? Thanks, man!
[JOJI]
I ain't givin' it away for free.
Okay, so what?
You want money or something?
I can't even afford a
basic pack of boosters!
[JOJI]
It's a tradin' card, remember?
Well, then, what do
you wanna trade for it?
It's simple. The card for Kaho!
[KAHO wailing]
[JOJI] Come on.
Pretty sweet deal, isn't it?
[KAHO]
No! Surely he wouldn't...!
Don't do it, Kanade!
No deal.
Kaho isn't a thing.
You can't do that. You can't
treat girls like they're things.
[KAHO] I actually thought
he might go for it.
I'm sorry.
He's so sweet.
Thank you, Kanade.
Oh my gosh! Why am I so happy?
Yeah, you're right.
I dunno what I was
thinkin', Kanade.
I apologize, Brother.
[KANADE] Well, least ya seein'
where I'm coming from.
Hey, are you makin'
fun of my accent?
[KANADE]
Nah. Just catchin' it from ya!
My accent ain't catchin'!
[laughing]
[KAHO] It's like they're
even closer now.
They must be such good friends.
Hey, you know what?
How can I help ya, Brother?
With the trading card
off the table now,
I've been thinking that, uh...
Maybe we should
all date together!
[KAHO]
Eh?
Wait, you mean the three of us?
You, me, and Kaho makes three!
[KAHO]
What? He can't be serious!
"You, me, and Kaho makes three"
sounds like some
stupid romance novel.
This is crazy.
Just because they're
getting along doesn't mean
I have to get along with them!
Listen, you and Kaho are
both really important to me,
so I figured what could be
better than all three of us
being able to hang
out with each other?
[KAHO]
Why does it hurt?
I know this kind of thing
happens all the time, but...
And I know it's not
the first time Kanade's
gotten things mixed up, either.
[ARASHI]
Uh-oh.
[KOTA whimpering]
From here on,
we'll be the best trio ever!
Yeah!
[KAHO]
Oh, no.
My heart... it's hurting.
[KANADE laughing]
[KAHO]
This isn't right.
[KANADE]
Huh?
[KAHO]
I wanted to be in a couple,
nd that's only two people,
not three.
[KANADE] I get that,
but I was just trying to think
about Joji's feelings.
[KAHO] But what about
my feelings, Kanade?
Not to mention
how you really feel.
What do you mean,
your feelings?
You love me, don't you?
[KAHO]
Yes, Kanade, I suppose I do.
But I love you, only you.
I don't want to be
forced to share the time
we spend together
playing with Joji,
and you should have
asked me about that.
You don't wanna play?
Well, then,
what do you wanna do?
[KAHO] Kanade, it's not
about what I wanna do.
The point I'm trying to make
is that I want to be special
for you alone.
And I want you to be
special for me alone, too.
I don't care about whatever
immature things you do
or whatever kiddy
stuff you say.
None of that matters as
long as I'm special to you.
But I'm starting to
get the feeling that...
I don't know, it's like you...
...it's like you don't love me.
Not at all.
[KAHO crying]
Wait, Kaho, are you crying?
Tell me where it hurts!
[TAGA]
It's her heart.
You hurt her heart.
[KANADE]
Taga?
Now before, when you
said I made her cry,
you hit me for doing it.
Remember?
But this time you're
the one who made her cry.
And you did it in a
much crueler way, too.
What are you talking about?
I wasn't being a bully!
[TAGA] No, but you don't
really love her and never did.
That's why she's crying.
[TAGA] In which case, I,
the actual adult around here...
...will take her with me.
[KAHO]
What is Taga trying to do?
Hey!
What's the big idea,
buttin' in on us?
Who the heck are you?
[TAGA] I could ask
you the same thing.
[KANADE]
This guy is my cousin, Taga.
How old?
[JOJI]
I'm in the sixth grade!
Of course you are.
What do you think
you're laughin' at?
Age don't matter none!
Besides, you can't
just take her!
It's like Kanade said,
Kaho ain't a thing!
She's not just something
that you can give and take!
[Don't worry, I don't intend
on taking her as a thing.
Oh, I'll be taking
her heart, as well.
In a way that a
little kid never could.
[KAHO]
Um...
[JOJI] What the heck do you
mean, "a way we never could"?
[KANADE] Because I can
do anything if I try!
[JOJI] And I'm a push comes
to shove kinda man, myself!
Big talk for kids who don't
know anything about women.
Will you stop it with
all the "um"ing already?
If you've got something
to say, then just say it.
God, you're annoying.
If that's true, if I'm
just so annoying to you,
why won't you write me off,
then, and leave me alone?
No one here asked
for you to jump in.
[TAGA]
Huh?
I guess you're not
taking the bait this time.
Is it possible the stupid girl
has learned something?
[KAHO]
What? Back off.
Kanade and I... we're having
an important discussion!
[TAGA chuckles]
An important discussion, is it?
Huh?
[KAHO]
Kanade?
[TAGA]
You must be so proud,
what, with elementary
kids fighting over you.
[laughs]
That's worth spying on. Right?
They can't tear
themselves away.
No! It's not like that!
Really? Then what
is it like, Kota?
[KAHO]
I'm getting spied on again?
What's wrong with these people?
They're all just so, so...
I do so know about women!
Me too! It's spelled W-O-Man!
[KAHO]
I can't!
I just can't!
[crying]
[KAHO] I'm not getting
through to him at all!
Taga's a jerk.
And everyone else thinks
all of this is fun.
I have no idea what
Kanade's thinking,
and I hate that I even care!
I did my best to put
my feelings into words,
but he's just not getting it.
[KAHO]
What do I do now?
What do I do?
Now, today's topic...
[KOTA] No, first I want
my trunks back, okay?
Who has them?
Question! Do you know
what the difference is
between a wiener
and a pee-pee?
Where did that come from?
I was just thinking there's
lots of words for it.
That's right. I've heard old
men call their thing a [ding].
Whenever my sister is changing
her little baby's dirty diapers,
she always calls it a pee-pee.
Anyway, can I get
my trunks back please?
That's a good theory.
Newborn boys have pee-pees.
While we have wieners!
And old guys have [ding]!
[KOTA]
I need my trunks!
[JOJI]
Well, that's cool!
So that means wieners change
names as they get bigger.
You mean like promotion
fish change names?
[KANADE]
What's a promotion fish?
Very good question.
They're fish whose names
change as they mature.
For example:
The buri yellowtail,
it starts off as wakashi ,
inada , warasa .
And then, its final
ultimate form is buri .
Whoa.
What I'm gettin' outta this
is we should be calling 'em
promotion wieners.
--Like this?
--[JOJI, TOM, KANADE] Ooh!
[KANADE]
Wait!
Think first.
I've heard people calling
wieners rods and poles
and bats and all kinds
of other stuff.
[TOM, JOJI, GIN]
Say what?
What about that, Kaz?
Teach us!
Clearly, they must have
evolved independently.
[JOJI, TOM, KANADE]
Ah!
Evolved independently?
That's so cool!
[GIN] You know,
I've heard a word, too.
It's a special term that has
something to do with wieners.
Let's see,
I think it's "erection."
"Erection"?
We got us a whole
new one now!
Wait! I think I heard Mom say
her clam dish was erectable!
[JOJI] Ooh, so it's
a kind of shellfish?
No, you're wrong! Wrong!
You know what that means.
It's the final evolution
of the wiener.
Erection!
[laughing]
[KOTA] Listen to me,
guys, you're so wrong!
And where are my trunks?
[RENREN]
Renren here!
Coming up on
First Love Monster .
[mumbling incoherently]
[RENREN]
All that, and more!
Next time:
"Hula-Hoop Hullabaloo"!
And now for a match!
Renren, paper, scissors!