[KAHO]
It's morning.
No matter how dark the night,
morning will always come.
[alarm ringing]
[knocking]
[KAHO]
Just a second!
[KANADE]
Yo!
You down for some breakfast?
[KAHO]
Oh, yes! I'm d--uh...
I'll be right there.
Cool! Hurry!
[KAHO]
I didn't think about that.
We live under the same roof,
so we'll probably see each other
first thing in the morning
all the time.
I should let you know...
It's nothing personal, but I'm
against you and Kanade dating.
[KAHO]
He should be.
I'm against me dating
a fifth grader, too.
What am I going to do?
[SHUGO]
Good morning!
You must be Miss Nikaido.
[KAHO]
Oh! Yes.
But please call me Kaho.
Sorry for not
greeting you earlier.
I'm your landlord,
Shugo Takahashi.
[KAHO]
Takahashi? Wait a minute...
[KAHO] Are you related
to Kanade, by chance?
Yeah. I'm his dad.
[KAHO]
Of course he is.
[recorder playing]
[KOTA]
Kanade, please knock it off!
Sorry, but he's always
loud in the morning.
No, it's totally fine.
He's always been
a rambunctious one.
But after his mom died
a couple of years back,
he started to become a
handful, to say the least.
C'mon, Shinohara.
Just act like you're
awake so he'll quit.
[KOTA]
Look, I'm up!
Stop! I'm getting
a headache now!
Just try to think of him
as your little brother,
and play with him
every now and then.
Yeah, of course.
[KAHO] Not like I can
tell you he's my boyfriend.
So sure, he might as well
be my little brother, too.
Why stop the weird now?
[groans]
[KAHO]
Um... hello?
You must be Kaho, right?
Oh, you're so cute!
Who's the cutest cutie?
You are! Yes, you are!
Such a cutie!
Behind you!
[ARASHI yells]
Except for the fact that
Chiaki's the cutiest cutie
in the whole entire world!
[KAHO]
What?
I have no idea what's going on!
FYI, that's Arashi Nagasawa.
He's a grad student
and just happens to be
Chiaki's boyfriend.
[ARASHI groaning]
You know there's a punishment
when your eyes stray like that.
[KAHO]
So they're together?
Thank you for the food!
[KAHO]
Hey. What's up?
Can I have your seaweed?
'Kay. Here.
[KANADE]
Thank you!
Yo, Kota, I want yours, too.
Well I already ate all of it!
[KANADE]
Greedy!
How about you, Arashi?
Yeah, sure.
I'll take your seaweed.
[KANADE]
No, that's not what I meant.
Sit down and stop begging.
But I--
One seaweed packet per person.
Understand me?
[KANADE]
Fine.
[KAHO giggles]
Kanade must really love
seaweed to beg for it.
So adorable!
[SHUGO]
Oh, that's right, Miss Kaho...
[KAHO]
Yes?
I can't believe I forgot.
I haven't explained the ins and
outs of the House to you yet.
[KAHO]
No.
[TAGA] I can take care of that
later if you'd like me to.
[SHUGO]
Yeah, thanks. That'd be great.
[KAHO] Well, thank you
in advance, Taga.
[KAHO] Wow, he really
seems like he's a nice guy.
[KANADE] So tell me. What do
people do when they're dating?
Come on! You gotta know!
[KAHO]
I'm going to die!
How can he just
shout that out...
Whoa, where on Earth
did that come from?
Well, actually...
[KAHO]
This is the end!
I bet I know.
He's been watching a lot
of those soap operas lately.
[SHUGO]
Of course.
The brain rotting TV again.
[KAHO]
Oh, good.
Wait a sec...
Did Taga's covering
for us actually work?
[KANADE]
Wait, I know.
Arashi, you're dating Chiaki,
so you gotta do something.
What do you guys do?
Well, I call her
every morning, and...
Call her?
[ARASHI] Yeah, I call her
when I leave the house, too.
Why? Can you not just text her?
[ARASHI] Because when
you're dating someone,
you want to hear their voice!
However, it doesn't seem
to matter much recently
considering I've been on
Chiaki's rejection list.
I wonder why!
Kinda creepy to call
me 90 times a day
when we, uh...
live in the same building!
I can't help myself, though.
I get all of three
feet away from you
and then immediately miss
the sound of your voice!
[CHIAKI] You get five
calls max from now on.
Okay, okay.
Five times for my baby!
Kanade. Arashi is not
a decent role model.
Please don't listen to him.
Okay. Then you tell me, Kota.
[KOTA gasps]
Who, me?
Well, you... you can, uh...
hold hands, I guess?
[CHIAKI] Kanade, asking a virgin
deluxe is even more useless.
[KANADE]
Virgin?
[KOTA]
No!
Don't make fun. That has
nothing to do with this!
But regardless,
you are a virgin, aren't you?
Hey, Kaho.
What's a virgin?
Young man!
That is not a question
you should ask a lady.
Eat your food, now!
[KANADE] Why won't you tell me?
You're so mean!
More importantly,
I thought I heard you were
supposed to hang out
with Gin and Tom this morning?
[KANADE]
Oh, that's right!
[TAGA] The landlord
usually makes our meals,
so just be sure to let
him know whenever you
decide to opt out.
[KAHO]
Right.
[TAGA] We have free
reign of the kitchen,
but make sure you
don't eat anything
without getting
permission first.
Oh, and if you keep
anything in the fridge,
put your name on it,
or it'll be gone.
Snacks or whatnot.
Okay.
[TAGA] As for the bath,
this is the schedule.
Write your name next to
whatever bathtime you'd like.
And yes, the bathroom
door does lock.
[KAHO]
Great.
I think that's
pretty much everything.
[KAHO] Thanks for doing this.
It was very kind of you.
Oh, no, it was nothing, really.
I almost forgot about
your welcome party!
What? A party?
[TAGA]
Of course.
We can have it in
my room later on today.
Yeah, okay.
That sounds great!
Wonderful!
We're all so happy
that you're here.
[KAHO]
Thank you so much.
[TAGA]
No problem. See ya later.
Yep. See you soon,
and thanks again!
[KAHO]
A welcome party?
It makes me a little nervous,
but it's so nice, too.
[SHUGO] Kaho, do you mind
putting those cardboard boxes
out by the trash?
No, I don't mind at all.
[SHUGO]
I'll be back.
I've got a few errands to run.
'Kay. I'll see you in a while!
[KAHO] What would Kanade's
dad do if he found out
I was dating his son?
His fifth-grade son,
to be exact.
[CHIAKI]
Indecent much?
Criminal? Maybe.
Perverted? Yeah.
[KAHO] Yeah, what he
doesn't know can't hurt me.
[KAHO squeals]
[KAHO]
What are you doing, Kanade?
Nothing! I like
upper arms, jeez!
Did you have to
sneak up on me?
[KANADE]
Can't I?
Not if you scare me.
Not like that.
You're right,
'cause you're my girlfriend.
[KAHO]
He called me his girlfriend.
Oh my gosh.
I think I'm blushing!
I shouldn't be touching a girl
unless it's my girlfriend.
And only if it's okay with her.
That's what I was taught.
[KAHO]
By whom?
My mom, silly.
Your mom said that? Really?
[KANADE]
Yep!
[KAHO] I still can't believe
this considerate guy
is in elementary school.
[TOM]
Kanade!
We're here for some
eleph-fun! Whoo!
Mr. Elephant,
your trunk is so long!
Long trunk!
Long trunk! Long wiener, too!
[ALL]
Long, long wiener, too!
Yay!
[KAHO] Or I totally believe
he's in elementary school.
[KANADE] Bamboo Primary's
jump rope competition
is early next week,
so we've gotta practice.
[KAHO]
Really? That sounds fun.
Uh-huh!
I'm gonna try to beat
the criss-cross record.
Criss-cross?
[NARRATOR] "Criss-cross"
is a highly difficult variation
on jumping rope,
wherein the jumper must
jump through the gap
formed where the
rope is crossed.
It is also called
double jump or speed jump
depending on the region.
Incidentally, we
have confirmed reports
that experiencing the
sting of a jump rope
against one's bare leg as
a child can directly lead
to increased
interest in masochism
upon reaching adulthood.
Trust me. I'm like
a criss-cross expert!
I can jump 30 times in a row!
I'll show you,
if you want me to!
[KAHO giggles]
Yeah. I'd love to see that.
I'm gonna practice
triple-unders until I own them!
Not me.
I'm gonna use my jump rope
to tie stuff up instead.
[KANADE]
What? Why?
Jumping is more fun!
Good morning, Kaho.
How're you?
[KAHO]
Fine, thanks.
Good morning.
Hey, you wanna
jump rope with us?
Well, uh...
[shrieks]
I would, but I still have
a lot of cleaning to do
after moving in and stuff, so...
Suit yourself.
But you should come
play when you're done!
[KAHO]
Yeah, I will.
For sure. When I'm done.
Now, off we go yodel-oh!
Now, off we godel-odel-oh.
Now, yodel-ay-pee-poo.
Later!
If you'll excuse us.
[KAHO]
Uh, yeah. Bye.
[giggles]
[sighs]
[ARASHI]
Well, that was a big sigh.
[KAHO]
Um... is this okay?
Oh, don't worry.
I go for "pretty girls" anyway.
Yeah, to be specific,
I like boys dressed as girls.
So I guess you could
say pretty-girl boys.
Huh?
[ARASHI]
Like Li'l Renren!
You know him, right?
Come here.
This is what I'm talking about.
[ARASHI]
Oh!
This is my entire collection
of Li'l Renren merchandise!
[laughing]
Ooh!
Oh.
It's so nice you have a hobby
you can devote yourself to.
I know, right?
I'm the luckiest ever!
OMG. I can't stand it!
Isn't Li'l Renren adorable?
I could lick them all over!
A little tee-hee right here.
A little ooh-hoo right there
where they're ticklish.
Oh, my fantasies
are in overdrive!
I'm breathless!
Oh oh oh oh!
I'm sorry.
Forgot myself for a sec.
You must be so scandalized.
[ARASHI]
You know what's great, though?
Chiaki still accepts me
just the way I am.
You understand, don't you?
Seems like you've got a
big enough heart to accept
your boyfriend exactly
the way he is, too.
But he's in the fifth grade.
[ARASHI] What is that,
a five-year age difference?
You know, Chiaki and I happen
to be five years apart, as well.
In the end, age has
nothing to do with it.
All you need is love.
That's it?
[ARASHI]
Yes, love! Love!
[KAHO]
I don't know.
It seems as if a loser
like me has no excuse
for being Kanade's girlfriend.
Seriously? Look, Kaho.
I feel like calling yourself a
loser is pretty rude to Chiaki
who accepts me this way,
but what do you think that
statement says about Kanade?
[KANADE] I heard if you call
yourself a loser too much,
you'll actually
wind up becoming one.
[KAHO]
He's right.
Plus, Kanade accepted
me the way I am
without even flinching.
Maybe I should just accept
him the way he is, too.
[KAHO] Arashi Nagasawa.
He's so sweet.
I hope I can repay him
for this advice one day.
I'm going to head
back to my room now.
But thanks for all
your help with every--
[ARASHI]
Oh...!
My Li'l Renren! Squee!
You're so frikkin cute!
My live on-the-air
costume change!
That's right after
these messages!
[ARASHI screams]
Just kidding!
Aren't I the worst?
[ARASHI whining]
[KAHO]
Finally made it!
They're gone?
[KANADE] Maybe to you,
but it's super precious to me.
[KAHO]
What are they talking about?
I wonder what could be
so precious to Kanade.
What is that old saying?
Joined at the something. Uh...
I know! It's joined at the nip!
Tom, what Kanade's thinking
of is "joined at the hip."
Yeah, joined at the hip!
That's what I was thinking of!
[KAHO]
Do I wanna know?
[GIN]
What if this precious treasure
suddenly went away tomorrow?
We need to have a
plan just in case, guys.
Yeah, shut up, man.
Why're you trying to scare us?
Just think.
You love it so much,
it could poke you in the butt
and you won't care.
"Eye." Could poke
you in the "eye."
I'm pretty sure that's
what he means, so...
Ah!
What's wrong with you, Gin?
That would really hurt bad!
So true! Eye or butt, bad!
[KAHO]
Hey, guys!
You seem to be having a
very serious conversation.
What are you talking about?
We're talking about our
most precious partners!
Partners?
[KANADE]
Hold up!
We shouldn't talk about
this in front of Kaho.
He's right.
We can discuss this
some other time.
[KAHO]
Oh.
Kanade's hiding something that
he feels like he can't tell me.
Hey, I'm really sorry.
It's just that none of us
want to be mean to you.
Because you're the only
one here without one.
A wiener, obviously.
Hey! There's a lady present.
We need to stop talking
about this right now!
What? I don't get it.
Stop talking about what?
[KAZ]
No more beep stuff.
Huh? I can't hear you.
[KAZ] Beep stuff!
Words that get beeped!
Nothing we're saying
should get beeped!
Come on, man, step up
and shout out "wiener"
like the rest of us do!
[KAZ]
I will do no such thing!
I'd give you one if
there was a way I could.
I only have one, though.
I'm sorry.
You would love it.
Wieners are the
best things ever.
[KAHO]
Nope. I'm good!
I don't want one!
Not at all!
[BOYS]
You don't want one?!
How can you say that
when our precious wieners
mean everything to us?!
So... was I wrong?
Because I really believed
that you of all people
would accept this
treasure we hold so dear.
But instead you
don't want a wiener,
and you didn't even have
to think about it first!
[KAHO]
What on Earth?
Why does that upset
Kanade so much?
Uhh, actually...
I do want a wiener, Kanade!
I do want one!
Of course you do!
[KAHO] Did I just say what I'm
pretty sure I think I just said?
On the bright side, at least
they're all smiling again.
Always find the silver lining.
[KAHO]
You know what?
I just realized that I never
got the chance to see you
jumping criss-cross
style earlier.
Well, I'm finished
with my lunch,
but we can hit up
the park later.
Criss-cross!
Criss-cross! Yeah!
That sounds like fun.
Oh, hey.
[TAGA]
Nice timing, Kanade.
I literally just saw
this ginormous ladybug
right outside my window.
No way!
Way. I think it had ten spots.
[KANADE]
A ten-spot ladybug? Cool!
Thanks! I'm gonna go catch
her before she gets away!
[laughs]
Ten-spot! Ten-spot! Ten-spot!
Yep, he's a kid all right.
Yeah. Yeah, that he is.
[KAHO] His eyes were twinkling
so much over one little ladybug!
So adorable.
[TAGA]
Well, then... shall we?
[KAHO]
Oh. Sure.
Funny...
I guess no one was able to come.
By the way,
how much should I
chip in for the party?
Oh, no.
I... I left my wallet
back in my room.
I'm gonna go grab it.
I'll be right back.
Taga?
Are you really that stupid?
You just waltzed
right in to the room
of some man you
barely even know.
[KAHO]
But... the welcome party...
Ha!
There is no welcome
party, idiot. Nothing.
You're a sheltered princess
who's never known
hardship before.
People like you make me sick.
And falling for Kanade
proves how stupid you are.
Don't pretend
you haven't fallen.
Getting all nervous and
flushed are a major tell.
You're strangely assertive.
And that makes me hate you more.
[FRIEND 2A] But Mom says I can't
come to your birthday party.
I know I promised you
that I would,
but I have to take it back.
Mom said our families belong
to different social classes,
and that means I
shouldn't play with you.
As if anyone would welcome
a pathetic little
princess like you.
Kanade?
This ladybug wasn't
even a little big, you jerk!
And it only has
seven spots, not ten!
Ah.
Well, my bad.
And with this forehead flick,
you have been forgiven.
[TAGA]
Okay, then why did you hit me?
She's crying.
You're making my
girlfriend cry, dude.
I'm just protecting her.
Don't make your girlfriend cry.
You gotta protect her.
[KAHO] Kanade, did your
mom teach you that, too?
[KAHO]
Well, now what do I do?
My monster just
keeps getting cooler.
And I really like it.
[KOTA]
Um...
My name is Kota Shinohara,
and I'm on duty today. So, uh...
[KANADE]
I got a question! Pick me!
Uh, well, since
you put your hand up...
What the heck's a virgin?
I mean, you're a virgin, right?
What does that mean?
[GIN, TOM]
Yeah, we wanna know, too!
Tell us what a virgin is!
Gah!
Why is my virginity such a big
deal to everyone now, huh?
[TAGA]
I can tell you what it means.
This virginity Kota possesses
is a fantastic thing.
[BOYS]
Huh?!
If he keeps it safe, he could
become a mage of sorts.
He could become a mage?
[TAGA]
Yes, and having had no attempts
on his virginity thus far,
Kota here is a pure virgin.
The king of virgins,
if you will.
[KANADE, GIN, TOM]
No way! Awesome!
Calm down!
It is not awesome.
In fact, I'd throw
it away if I could.
[KANADE, GIN, TOM]
You'd throw it away?
If you don't want it,
give that thing to me.
[KOTA] Nope.
No, I'm not gonna do that.
Hey, that's not fair!
What if I want Kota's virginity?
[KOTA] Well, you
can't have it, Kanade!
Cool. Does that mean
I get it, then?
No, not you either!
Hold on. What is going on here?
[KAZ]
It's unclear.
Is a virginity worth getting
so worked up over?
Oh! If so,
does that mean you
want to be a virgin, Kaz?
Yes! Let's all be virgins!
Virgins forever!
Spoiler alert.
You guys are already virgins.
[BOYS]
Huh?!
[BOYS chattering, laughing]
I think I should
use this moment
to come out of the proverbial
shadows myself.
I'm totally a virgin, too.
[ALL]
What?
[KOTA]
But you have a girlfriend!
[ARASHI] Chiaki's the
pretty girl that I love,
but I only desire
pretty-girl boys!
[ALL]
Awesome!
[RENREN] Everyone's favorite
Renren here!
Coming up on
First Love Monster :
Blah blah blah blah,
primary school years,
blah blah blah,
Kasumi House, blah.
All that and more!
Next time: "It's My First."
And now for a match!
Renren, paper, scissors!