It's simple.
The card for Kaho!
[KANADE] Maybe we
should all date together!
You, me, and
Kaho makes three!
Don't worry.
I'll take her with me.
[KAHO]
I just can't!
[KANADE] Kota!
Gimme your seaweed.
Again? But I already
opened the packet.
That's fine. I don't care.
Gimme your seaweed.
Okay. I suppose
I can let you have it.
Yay! Thank you!
Kaho, gimme yours, too.
Uh-oh.
I bet Kaho's still mad at you.
Mad at me for what?
[CHIAKI] You made her
cry literally yesterday.
Yeah, I know,
but it's morning.
You wake up fine
the day after a fight.
That only works for children,
but I suppose it's too much
to expect a mere child
to understand a woman's heart.
Understand a woman's heart?
Please tell me you
delivered your letter, Yuki.
What? So you really
sent that love letter?
Spill it!
Who'd you give it to?
Uh... I, um... uh...
Okay, we'll guess, then.
First, she's got really
high standards.
And that's with an
emphasis on the visual!
It has to be a boy
in this class, doesn't it?
[YUI]
Is it Tom?
[LEIA] No, he gets
too much attention.
There was another TV
special on his stupid-huge
family yesterday.
I bet even dates with him
would be broadcast live.
Ew, no thank you.
[LEIA]
Ooh, could it be Gin?
I was too busy.
Last night, transmissions from
the SM78 nebula needed me.
[TOM]
Were you summoning UFOs?
No, he's so gross.
It definitely can't be him.
So gross.
[LEIA]
What about Kanade?
Oh, son of a rat.
I totally left my
backpack somewhere.
--What are ya gonna do?
--Just wait.
He'll find his way home.
[YUI]
Yeah. I don't think so.
Besides, she can't like him.
He's already got a girlfriend--
one that's in high school.
Crazy, right?
From what I've been told,
they're living together
in the same house, too!
[GIRLS]
What?!
Therefore,
she has to be after
the best guy in class,
and that happens to be...
Oh, Master Kaz, it's you!
Take your seats, everyone.
Since the teacher's out,
we can use this time
to discuss what event
we'd like to host during
the school sports festival.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Quiet, please!
Raise your hand if you
have something to say.
[KANADE]
I do!
[KAZ]
Kanade Takahashi. Go ahead.
I think another student
forgot something at my desk
because this isn't mine.
Wow, this writing sure is tiny.
"I will be waiting for you at
the equipment shed after class.
Come alone."
That was no accident.
It's a challenge, my friend.
One you can accept,
because I've got your back!
So, c'mon, who's the wise guy?
Must be from some girl.
The writing is pretty.
[FEMALE STUDENT 6A]
Is it me, or...
[FEMALE STUDENT 6B]
Its a love letter!
[FEMALE STUDENT 6D]
Totally a love letter!
[KAZ] Kanade! You are
gravely lacking in delicacy!
[KANADE]
Deli-casie?
Is that a lunchmeat?
No, it's not!
It means you're being
cruel to read a love letter
in front of the entire class!
[KANADE]
Wait... This is a love letter?
That sucks. Wish it coulda
been a challenge, man.
Well, if it really is
a love letter...
Sorry, but I've already
got a girlfriend.
[TOM]
Hold on, Kanade.
Didn't you two have a
fight yesterday, though?
Have you already made up?
I guess not.
She ate my breakfast
seaweed this morning.
[FEMALE STUDENT 6E]
What, they're fighting?
[MALE STUDENT 6A]
Are they gonna break up?
That's enough, guys!
Kanade Takahashi
Talk Time is over.
We're going to move on
to the topic at hand:
the sports festival.
By majority decision,
for this year's sports festival,
we have elected
to play dodge ball.
I'm sick of stinkin'
dodge ball. Boo.
Well, too bad for you.
Some students in this
room have matured so fast
that their physical prowess
differs from the rest of us,
so they're just going
to have to suck it up.
Yeah.
I guess you are
at a disadvantage.
Height-wise, I mean.
[KAZ]
How dare you?!
I'm well on my way into
my second growth period!
There's no need to be hateful!
You apologize
to Kaz immediately!
That's right, apologize!
Apologize, apologize, apologize!
You're the worst, ever, Kanade!
Calm down, everyone.
There's no reason to be angry.
Pardon me for
losing my composure.
It was terribly juvenile.
How embarrassing.
It appears as though I don't
only need to grow in my height.
My patience could use some
more development, as well.
Oh my gah, he's so cool!
Oh, Master Kaz,
you're so grown-up and cool!
[GIN] That's a five-year
class president for you.
He'll probably be our future
student council president, too.
As for me,
I am destined to take over
my family's OBGYN practice
and provide exams to
all the girls in this class,
eventually guiding
them through childbirth!
[FEMALE STUDENTS]
Gross!
[TOM] Kanade, don't forget
your backpack again!
[KANADE]
Got it!
[TOM] Man, those girls
were super mad at you
in today's class
meeting, weren't they?
[KANADE]
I guess,
but I don't care if those
girls like me or not.
[GIN] You know, lately
I've gotten so used
to being called gross
it's actually starting
to feel awesome.
Seriously?
I really want the
girls to like me!
Popularity?
Yeah, you should give that
up as long as Kaz is around.
[JOJI]
Kanade!
[KANADE]
Brother!
Howdy do!
[TOM]
What's the deal?
Why didn't you tell us your
cousin was still in town,
Kanade?
[KANADE] So, my cousin
is still in town.
[TOM]
Huh?
[JOJI] I been waitin'
for ya all day, Kanade!
Thought I'd beat some manly
spirit into ya, y'know?
Uh no, I don't know.
Well, if you're a man,
you can't go makin' Kaho darlin'
cry like that, ya hear me?
So I'mma teach you
a valuable lesson.
You ready to lose
a tennis match to me?
[KANADE] You wanna start
a fight? 'Cuz I'll finish it!
Bring it on, Brother!
[JOJI]
Careful what ya wish for!
Hi-yah!
Hey, I have no idea how
I should be keeping score.
Neither do I.
But fear not, my friend.
This battle of theirs
has gone far beyond
the concept of points.
[KANADE]
Here it comes!
My killer move!
[recorder playing]
[KANADE]
The Tornado Serve of Destiny!
[JOJI] Nice trick droppin' my
guard by playing purty music
on your recorder there.
I shoulda' been prepared
for somethin' like that.
But it ain't no thang.
I'll just sack this here ball
back to ya faster than ever!
Best get ready,
'cause my Ballsack Serve
is comin' atcha!
[KANADE groans]
Well, d'ya learn your lesson?
Y'ain't never gonna beat me,
and now ya know it.
Trust I got too good a handle
on your weaknesses, cousin!
[KANADE]
Weaknesses?
I don't have any
weaknesses, bro!
Take it back!
[JOJI]
Fess up!
Ya once promised a girl
you'd marry her, didn't ya?
[KANADE]
That's news to me!
[JOJI] It's fact.
Ya said the words, "Marry me!"
[KANADE]
I totally didn't do that.
[JOJI]
Did, too. I heard it myself.
[KANADE]
When?
What hour, what minute,
what second,
how many times had the
Earth turned around, huh?
[JOJI] I'd say it turned about
twenty thousand times or so!
--[KANADE] What hour was it?
--[JOJI] Happy hour!
This battle's kind
of impressing me.
D'you say depressing?
Because I agree.
[KANADE, JOJI panting]
I tell ya what, ya give
purty good, Kanade.
You, too, Brother.
[JOJI]
Still gotta say, though...
It ain't becomin' in
the least to go and forget
all about your betrothed.
You're confused.
Nothing you say makes sense.
Dude, ya proposed to Yukie!
You know, my ma!
Yeah, but that was
when I was a kid.
[JOJI] Well, guess I got to
know your manly spirit better
with that tennis match!
Not that it matters none.
You're still failing big time
when it comes to
bein' a boyfriend.
I'm failing?
Not your fault.
It's like ya just don't
understand a woman's heart.
Heard that before.
The girls in my class
say the same thing.
Maybe women are
just really angry people.
Namiko's always in my
face about dirty dishes
and using too much shampoo.
I don't get women at all.
Well, from what
I've been told,
they're all really complicated.
You know, kinda like
figuring out fractions.
[ARASHI] Are we speaking
of a woman's heart?
I can certainly help you
learn more about that, boys.
[ARASHI]
And with that...
Top-secret mission!
This meeting of the Women's
Heart Research team
is now in session!
[KANADE]
I can feel air on my butt!
I still don't get how
this is gonna help us
understand a woman's heart.
I reckon dressin' up like
this is the best way, though.
I mean, how ya gonna know
what women hafta go through
unless you're actually
tryna be one?
Now... It's time for you to
take your shot, young man.
Tee-hee.
[TOM]
I think Joji may be right.
Wow, I can't believe I'm already
starting to know women better!
Fair Gin's channeling
full-throttle!
The surging cosmic radio
waves are leaving a tingle
throughout my entire body!
[ARASHI moaning]
You guys look amazing!
Ah! Glorious! Just wonderful!
To think I'd have the chance to
see my secret stash of costumes
come to life like this!
[KOTA] Hold on...
If I could have a moment...
This also has absolutely
nothing to do with me, right?
So why... why me?
You're killing it!
Those tears in your
eyes are gold!
The rest of us
are here, too!
For real. What about
taking our pictures?
Whoa. This must be
how insecure feels.
Check out Miss Kota,
hoarding all of the praise!
[KOTA]
Don't get mad at me!
I didn't ask him
to praise anything!
[ARASHI]
It's okay.
You can't help that pretty face
or how charming you look
when you're embarrassed!
Like the boys over there,
most guys put a skirt on
and get over their nervousness
almost immediately.
They're just clothes, after all.
Oh, that's gotta hurt!
Kanade has grabbed
Joji's back in a cobra twist
and is, in fact, twisting.
Joji is handling it well by
staying close to the ground!
[KANADE yells]
[TOM] Kanade's been flipped
in a figure-four hold!
But not for long.
No way Joji's stopping here!
It's the Tickler Grip!
Poor Kanade! That's gotta
tickle so bad it hurts!
[KANADE laughing]
[JOJI]
You're up, kid!
And, both wrestlers have been
replaced with their teammates.
Ooh! Big move!
Tom catches Gin in a scissor
sweep right off the bat.
And now, he's movin'
into an electric massage!
[NARRATOR] The electric
massage is a secret,
forbidden technique
in elementary-school kung fu.
Its history dates back to
before the common era,
when, while wrestling in
an ancient Olympics,
one "Elektros Masáz" began
persistently massaging
his opponent's crotch
with his foot.
Even now, its mix
of pleasure and danger
give the move a strong following
as the ultimate
"skinship" between boys.
[ARASHI] C'mon, your clothes
are going to get all wrinkled.
That's enough wrestling.
Please stop!
So, um...
I'm gonna go back to
my room now, okay?
What? Already?
Aw, ya can't go yet.
Don't be such a girl.
Have some fun!
No, thanks. Just because
it's fun for you
doesn't mean that it's fun
for everyone else.
You can really hurt a person
by forcing your ideas
or plans on them.
It feels like you don't care.
[KAHO] I don't wanna be forced
to share the time we spend
together playing with Joji,
and you should have
asked me about that.
I don't like doing this.
It's not fun for me at all!
Why didn't you just say no?
Hey, in a sense,
I feel as if he's got more of a
woman's heart than any of us do.
[KANADE]
Of course she's mad.
I remember now.
Something else
my mom told me.
Don't ever force someone to do
what they don't want to do.
Ever.
If Kota isn't having fun,
we shouldn't try to
make him play with us
if he doesn't like it.
[JOJI]
I get that.
Real grown up, Kanade!
[ARASHI]
But he looked so adorable!
Why do those committee
meetings always run so long?
[Well then quit
being a baby about it!
If you hate wearing that so
much, take it off already.
[TOM, GIN]
I see London, I see France!
[laughing]
[KOTA]
Oh, no!
I'll never get married now!
I guess they must
all be upstairs.
I wonder why.
Okay, where are they?
[KAZ yells]
[KAZ]
Tears?
My apologies, Miss!
[KAZ]
She must've dropped this.
[KAZ] "You are three kinds
of sweet-tart berries."
[KAZ]
"Your eyes are blueberries.
[KOTA]
Your lips, raspberries.
Though I want to be
by your side always,
your fruits are far
out of reach."
[KAZ]
What is this?
Wait, please!
[KAHO]
I'm home!
Kaho!
Did you see that girl?
She just ran down the stairs.
[KAHO]
No, I didn't see a girl.
I didn't see anyone.
But she was right here.
[KAHO]
What did you need with her?
I, uh... I don't exactly know.
But... I do know I
want to see her again.
So badly. So badly, I'm shaking.
I wanna know why she
was crying. Can I help?
And stupidly enough,
it's all I can think about.
What is this thing
that I'm feeling?
You're small,
but you are pretty cute.
[KAHO] Sounds to me
like it's your first love.
My first love?
Mm-hmm.
I recognize what
you're describing,
because that's pretty
much how I felt
the first time
that I met Kanade.
I understand now.
That girl is my very first love.
Hey, Kaz!
What took ya so long, man?
I just, um...
Forgive me. I seem
to have fallen in love.
In love?
[KAZ] Yes, with the owner
of this poetry journal.
I do believe her tears and pure
heart have changed me forever.
This must be it.
This must be love.
Sounds good to me.
I mean, still not real clear,
but I'm happy for you. Congrats!
Oh, thank you!
I get it now.
I finally understand how you
and Kaho have been feeling!
Uh-oh, the most popular
guy with the girls is in love!
Heads up, the girls in
class are gonna freak out.
So, uh, speaking of girls,
I'm just curious why you're
dressed up like that.
I'm sorry, but we
can't answer you.
We're in the middle of
a top-secret mission.
[KAHO]
Of course you are.
Well, don't let me keep you.
As you were.
[YUI]
This is it. Takahashi's house.
So are they like
living together, or not?
Has anyone seen anything yet?
[TAGA]
Can I help you?
[overlapping chatter]
[TAGA]
Right. It's getting dark.
Be careful, ladies.
[YUKA, YUI]
Boys that aren't boys anymore
are the best boys ever!
I swear, women even start
out annoying as hell.
[MAFUYU]
What's the big idea, Kanade?
Goodness gracious, it's time
for your tutoring, Mister!
C'mon. Sorry, boys,
it's time to go home.
Okay!
[MAFUYU] You need to
change clothes first, though.
What are you even wearing?
Shugo will never trust
me to tutor you again
if I let you walk around
in that fashion disaster.
And I'm not gonna
let that happen!
[KANADE]
Hey, Mafuyu.
What would you do
if you made someone
who means a lot
to you really mad?
[MAFUYU]
Apologize, apologize, apologize
till you're blue in the face!
Sliding kowtow, jumping kowtow,
rolling kowtow, flip kowtow.
[KANADE] I'm afraid she still
wouldn't forgive me after that.
Wow, tough call.
Ooh! Give yourself a punishment!
When she watches
you overcome it,
that should prove to
her how serious you are.
[inhales]
[MAFUYU]
If you want, give it to me.
You could punish me.
Oh, yeah!
Get angry, Shugo!
Get angry and hurt me
because I'm trash.
I'm garbage! [growling]
Yeah. Cool.
[KAHO]
He's in elementary school.
He can't love at
the same speed you can.
Which should tell you something.
[KANADE]
Kaho!
Oh, hello there, Kanade.
I think we need to talk, okay?
[KAHO]
He thinks we need to talk?
In a good way or a bad way?
Who am I kidding?
It's never in a good way.
So I've been thinking
a lot, like, about you.
And, you know, about like what
a good man is supposed to be.
I've decided to
hula-hoop for you.
Two hundred rotations.
Sorry, what?
[KANADE] It's to punish
myself for not being able
to understand how
the woman I love feels.
Did he say the woman he loves?
Is that me?
My current record
is 175 rotations.
If I make it to 200,
will you please forgive me
for being stupid yesterday?
You know, because you respect
my manly spirit and all?
[KAHO]
Are you serious?
I will do this. I will.
I don't want to let you
go without trying.
[KAHO] This is so surreal,
but go for it, Kanade.
[KAHO]
You're almost at 200!
So close!
You can do it, Kanade.
You can do it!
195, 196, 197...
Kaho...
...it's over.
[KANADE]
My heart is a drumbeat!
I may not be able to see, but I
can still drum like a rock star!
What a filthy Cinderella!
You disgust me.
Oh, Detective!
I can't hear you!
Again, with feeling!
Yes, Professor, sir!
I am just a clumsy,
slow, and stupid
single-celled water
flea with feeling!
[KAZ]
This is awful.
Who would put sea urchins
in my toe shoes?
[CHIAKI] My blood
is boiling-hot magma!
Touch me and you'll get burned!
[BOYS crying]
All right, boys!
Humiliated now?
Yes, sir, yes, we are!
[NARRATOR] Dazzling
drama doesn't disappoint,
all on the next
First Love Monster !
Narrator out.