Klaus:
RESOLUS WAS ATTACKED
BY MOBILE SUITS?
DAMN FEDERATION...
ATTACKING WITHOUT
ANY WARNING LIKE THAT.
I HEARD THERE WERE
NEW MODEL MOBILE SUITS
MIXED IN WITH
THE ENEMY FORCES.
MAYBE WE SHOULD...
LOOK KLAUS,
THESE GUYS ARE SERIOUS.
I THINK IT'S BEST WE POSTPONE
THE RESCUE OPERATION AT PROUD.
NO. IN FACT,
I THINK WE SHOULD PUSH
FOR AN EARLIER START.
A LOT OF OUR COMRADES' LIVES
ARE ON THE LINE.
(Tense sigh)
I'M SORRY, BUT WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO LOSE THEM.
I UNDERSTAND.
I'LL CONTACT THE RESCUE TEAM
AND TELL THEM
THAT THE OPERATION'S
BEEN RESCHEDULED.
PLEASE DO THAT.
HMM.
Klaus:
DAMN A‐LAWS!
Spokesperson:
THE FEDERATION GOVERNMENT
HEREBY ANNOUNCES
THE ACTIVATION OF
A PEACEKEEPING FORCE
UNDER GOVERNMENT CONTROL,
IN ORDER TO ELIMINATE
ANTI‐GOVERNMENT ELEMENTS.
ACTING IN COOPERATION WITH
THE FEDERAL SECURITY AGENCY,
PEACEKEEPERS WILL EFFICIENTLY
BEGIN OPERATIONS TO‐‐
Kati:
HEADQUARTERS
HAS JUST INFORMED ME
THEY WANT TO TRANSFER ME
TO THE AUTONOMOUS
PEACEKEEPING FORCE.
DO YOU PLAN ON GOING?
IT MIGHT NOT BE
SUCH A BAD IDEA
TO TAKE A CLOSER LOOK
AT THESE A‐LAWS
THAT'S A GROUP
THAT HAS TOO MANY SECRETS.
I'D BE GRATEFUL IF YOU KEPT
ME INFORMED OF YOUR FINDINGS.
I ALWAYS INTENDED TO.
LATER, THEN.
YEAH.
WAS THAT
COLONEL MANNEQUIN?
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
WHAT DID SHE WANT?
MORE IMPORTANTLY,
HAVE YOU GIVEN ANY THOUGHT TO
THE MATTER WE DISCUSSED EARLIER?
(Gasps)
NO, NOT YET.
THERE'S NO NEED TO
RUSH ANYTHING.
TAKE YOUR TIME
AND THINK IT OVER.
Miyasaka:
THAT'S GOOD.
STEADY... STEADY...
STOP! RIGHT THERE
IS JUST PERFECT!
(Relieved sigh)
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE GETTING
PRETTY GOOD AT THIS JOB, ROOKIE!
I'VE BEEN HERE
HALF A YEAR ALREADY.
WHEN ARE YOU GONNA STOP
CALLING ME ROOKIE,
MY NAME IS
SAJI CROSSROAD‐‐
(Alarmed gasp)
EDDIE MIYASAKA RIGHT?
ON SUSPICION OF
CONSPIRING WITH KATHARON,
YOU ARE HEREBY‐‐
(Grunts)
BASTARD!
DAMN!
MR. MIYASAKA!
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?!
I'M TAKING YOU IN, TOO!
ME?! WHAT'D I DO?!
(Cries in pain)
(Choking)
Saji:
WAIT A MINUTE! WON'T YOU EVEN
TELL ME WHAT I'VE DONE?!
PLEASE! STOP IT!
IT'S CONFIRMED, IT LOOKS LIKE
THE FEDERATION'S
NEW SPACE CRUISER IS MAKING
ITS WAY TOWARDS LAGRANGE 4.
IT'S JUST LIKE
WANG LIU MEI REPORTED.
MAYBE THIS WILL‐‐
I'M GOING OUT
WITH SERAVEE.
WELL, ROGER THAT!
HE'LL COME.
IF HE'S STILL ALIVE,
I KNOW HE'LL COME.
(Men grunting)
(Straining)
FORCED TO DO HARD LABOR
IN HIGH GRAVITY!
WITHOUT BEING ABLE TO USE
ANY MACHINES!
(Collapsing groan)
ARE YOU OKAY?
DON'T STOP WORKING, R81!
BUT LOOK!
DON'T WASTE YOUR TIME!
IF YOU WANT TO LIVE,
SHUT UP AND KEEP WORKING!
GET BACK TO WORK, R‐81!
(Groans)
DISTANCE,
2300 TO PROUD.
MAINTAIN GN PARTICLE DISPERSAL
AT NORMAL LEVELS.
COLONEL ZHEJIANG,
I UNDERSTAND
WE'VE FOUND THE KATHARON VESSEL.
YES, SIR.
A RECON UNIT DETECTED IT.
WE ARE CURRENTLY
TRACING ITS COURSE.
SO THEY ARE HEADING TO
PROUD AFTER ALL.
WHAT'S THE CURRENT STATUS
OF OUR NEW AUTOMATONS?
ALL UNITS ARE
PREPARED FOR DEPLOYMENT, SIR.
MMM.
COMMENCE THE OPERATION
TO DESTROY
THE ANTI‐GOVERNMENT FORCES!
PREPARE TO LAUNCH
AHEAD TEAM ONE.
PREPARE TO
LAUNCH AHEAD TEAM ONE.
AUTOMATON CONTAINER
IS NOW CONNECTED TO AHEAD.
UNITS REPORTING NO
ABNORMALITIES, ALL GREEN.
CAPTAIN ZININ.
THIS WILL BE WARRANT OFFICER
HALEVY'S FIRST SORTIE.
JUST LET HER GET A FEEL
FOR THE BATTLEFIELD.
ROGER.
ZININ TEAM,
READY AND LAUNCHING!
(Thinking)
IS IT BEING TARGETED?
THIS PLACE, TOO.
(Men straining)
I CAN'T LET THIS BEAT ME!
AS LONG AS
I'M IN SPACE,
THEN MAYBE ONE DAY,
LOUISE...
YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE EX‐MILITARY.
ARE YOU A MEMBER
OF KATHARON, TOO?
I'VE GOT NOTHING TO DO
WITH THEM!
JUST HAPPENED
TO GET CAUGHT UP?
STILL, THINGS COULD BE
A WHOLE LOT WORSE!
AND WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
YOU'LL FIND OUT
SOON ENOUGH.
HURRY UP
WITH THE EVACUATION!
THE OPERATION'S
ABOUT TO START!
R‐RIGHT!
SOMETHING'S WRONG
WITH MY SUIT.
(Surprised cry)
WHAT HAPPENED?
(Struggling gasp)
(Startled gasp)
WHAT "OPERATION"?
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
ANSWER ME.
(Gasps)
I DON'T KNOW.
WE WERE JUST GIVEN ORDERS TO
EVACUATE IMMEDIATELY!
HEY YOU!
HOLD ON!
YOU'RE NOT JUST GOING TO
LEAVE ME HERE, ARE YOU?!
(Crash)
(Surprised gasp)
WHAT'S THAT?
REALDO TEAM HAS COMPLETED
INITIAL OPERATION!
GOOD!
TIME TO GET
THE RESCUE MISSION UNDERWAY!
(Men muttering)
(Screaming)
FIND THE GRAVITY SYSTEM FOR
BLOCK SEVEN,
AND THEN HACK INTO IT!
ROGER THAT!
NOW TAKING CONTROL!
(Men screaming)
(Groans)
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THE GRAVITY!
THEY'VE COME
TO PICK US UP!
HUH?
OUR COMRADES ARE HERE!
COME ON, HURRY!
CAPTAIN! CONFIRMING
MOBILE SUITS RIGHT ABOVE US!
THEY FEDERATION?!
ONE OF THEM'S
A NEW MODEL!
(Grunts)
THAT MEANS
THEY'RE A‐LAWS.
(Screaming)
HUH?
ENEMY FORCES!
LIEUTENANT ALAGGA,
ENGAGE THE ENEMY.
ROGER.
WARRANT OFFICER HALEVY,
WAIT RIGHT HERE.
AS ACCORDING TO PLAN,
I'LL PROCEED WITH
THE PERFORMANCE TEST
FOR THE NEW AUTOMATONS.
Pilot:
IT'S TOO FAST!
Zinin:
I'VE REACHED THE TARGET POINT.
RELEASING CONTAINER.
NOW COMMENCING ACTIVATION
OF THE NEW AUTOMATONS.
(Machines whirring)
(Men shouting)
(Rapid gunfire)
MILITARY AUTOMATONS?!
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
(Surprised gasp)
(Panicked screaming)
(Gasps)
Setsuna:
ANTI‐PERSONNEL WEAPONS?
A‐LAWS MUST BE DOING THIS!
(Beeping and whirring)
(Rapid gunfire)
(Groans)
(Frightened panting)
(Determined grunt)
(Grunts)
(Gasps)
(Panting)
Setsuna:
GET BACK!
(Yells)
(Heavy breathing)
Setsuna:
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
(Gasps)
I'M GRATEFUL.
HUH?
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
COULD YOU BE
SETSUNA F. SEIEI?
AND YOU'RE SAJI CROSSROAD.
(Gasps)
WE'RE GOING!
FEDERATION DOG!
Alagga:
UNIT THREE?
NOT BAD.
Zinin:
UNIT THREE,
THAT WAS A GOOD CALL.
(Shallow breathing)
SETSUNA, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING OUT HERE?
JUST KEEP QUIET.
(Nervous gasp)
(Automaton approaching)
YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
(Gasps)
THIS WAY!
NOTHING'S CHANGED.
NOT ONE DAMN THING HAS CHANGED
IN ALL THIS TIME!
A READING
ON THE E‐SENSOR?
ENEMY REINFORCEMENTS!
THIS ISN'T WHAT WE WERE AFTER!
I DIDN'T WANT THIS,
AND NEITHER DID LOCKON!
NOT A WORLD LIKE THIS!
Setsuna:
YOUR HELMET.
Saji:
HUH?
OH, RIGHT.
(Gasps)
(Stunned gasping)
Alagga:
CAPTAIN! THAT SILHOUETTE!
YEAH.
AND THOSE GN PARTICLES.
(Gasps)
THE NUMBER OF AUTOMATONS
IN THERE...
IT'S DECREASING!
WHAT THE...?!
Alagga:
CAPTAIN! ABOVE US!
(Surprised cry)
THAT'S A...!
(Shocked gasp)
G‐GUNDAM!
HMM.
IT'S EXIA.
GUNDAM EXIA.
Saji:
SETSUNA.
HOW COULD YOU?
(Panting heavily)
MY HEAD IS JUST...!
Zinin:
SO IT'S CELESTIAL BEING,
IS IT?!
WHY WAIT TILL NOW
TO MAKE AN APPEARANCE?!
Setsuna:
I'LL DESTROY YOU.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO
DESTROY YOU.
ALL OF YOU OUT THERE
WHO DO THINGS LIKE THIS!
I'LL ELIMINATE YOU
ALL BY MYSELF!
YOU MAY BE A GUNDAM,
BUT YOU'RE FIVE YEARS OLD!
YOU'RE NO MATCH
FOR MY AHEAD!
(Grunts)
UNIT THREE, COVERING FIRE!
HUH?
WARRANT OFFICER HALEVY,
WHAT'S WRONG?!
(Heavy panting)
Zinin:
NEVER MIND, THE TWO OF US
CAN TAKE CARE OF IT!
I LOST A LOT OF FRIENDS
TO YOU BASTARDS!
(Metal crashing)
AND THIS IS MY CHANCE...
(Setsuna grunts)
...TO AVENGE THEM!
(Metal grinding)
(Frustrated gasp)
YOUR TIME IN THIS WORLD
HAS ALREADY ENDED!
(Frustrated growl)
I'VE GOT YOU NOW, GUNDAM!
(Gasp)
Alagga:
WHAT THE...?!
(Gasps)
THAT LOOKS LIKE A...
GUNDAM!
Alagga:
I GOTCHA!
WHAT?!
THAT'S A GN FIELD!
Alagga:
THERE'S A FACE ON ITS BACK!
(Alagga screaming)
Zinin:
WE'RE WITHDRAWING!
WARRANT OFFICER HALEVY!
UNIT THREE,
RESPOND IMMEDIATELY!
(Grunts)
DAMN IT.
Tieria:
I KIND OF FIGURED
YOU'D BE TRACKING
THE A‐LAWS' ACTIVITIES.
LONG TIME NO SEE,
SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
TIERIA...
ERDE.
Mileina:
MR. ERDE HAS LOCATED EXIA!
SETSUNA, SO YOU WERE
ON PROUD THEN.
MISS WANG'S INFORMATION
WAS RIGHT ON THE MONEY!
I BET HE'S GONNA BE SURPRISED
WHEN HE SHOWS UP
AND SEES YOU ON
THE BRIDGE, MR. LASSE.
YEAH, I IMAGINE SO.
SO, YOU'RE ALIVE AFTER ALL,
SETSUNA.
NOW WE CAN TRY OUT
EXIA'S SOLAR REACTOR.
GUNDAMS SHOWED UP
AT PROUD?
WELL THEN, I GUESS WE OWE THEM
A DEBT OF GRATITUDE.
THANKS TO THEM WE WERE ABLE TO
RESCUE OUR COMRADES
WHO WERE
STILL ALIVE IN THERE.
BESIDES, THIS IS A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY.
YOU KNOW THERE'S A POSSIBILITY
THAT THEY COULD TARGET US
FOR AN ARMED INTERVENTION.
NO.
AFTER ALL,
THEY'RE THE KIND OF PEOPLE
WHO SHARE THE SAME AMBITIONS
AND IDEALS AS WE DO.
IT'S BEEN FOUR YEARS,
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
VERY DIFFERENT ABOUT YOU.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED ONE BIT.
YOU LOOK EXACTLY THE SAME.
I GET THAT A LOT.
HMM.
SO, DOES THIS GUNDAM
BELONG TO CELESTIAL BEING?
Tieria:
NATURALLY.
Saji: (Angrily)
SETSUNA F. SEIEI!
HAVE YOU ALWAYS BEEN
THE PILOT OF THAT GUNDAM?!
SAJI CROSSROAD.
ANSWER ME!
YES.
THAT MEANS...
YOU WERE INVOLVED
FIVE YEARS AGO!
YES, I WAS.
HMPH.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'VE DONE?!
BECAUSE OF WHAT
YOU WERE DOING
A LOT OF PEOPLE DIED
WHO DIDN'T HAVE TO!
AND YOU'RE THE ONES
RESPONSIBLE!
BECAUSE OF YOU GUYS,
THE PERSON I LOVED
WAS INJURED,
AND HER FAMILY AND RELATIVES
WERE KILLED!
AND THEN ALL I HAD LEFT
WAS MY SISTER,
BUT SHE CROSSED PATHS
WITH CELESTIAL BEING,
AND SHE WAS KILLED, TOO!
(Sobbing)
I LOST LOUISE...
AND MY SISTER!
THEY'RE BOTH GONE NOW!
(Sobbing)
SAY SOMETHING!
(Furious grunt)
YOU GIVE THEM BACK!
GIVE THEM BACK TO ME.
BOTH OF THEM!
(Screaming)
GIVE THEM BACK TO ME!
Zhejiang:
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
GUNDAMS WOULD STAND IN OUR WAY?
A SPLENDID TURN OF EVENTS.
THEIR APPEARANCE
MAKES OUR ORGANIZATION
ALL THE MORE NECESSARY.
(Nervous gasping)
HMPH.
WHY IS SOMEONE LIKE THIS
EVEN IN THE A‐LAWS?
Ribbons:
LOUISE HALEVY.
I'M PLEASED FOR YOU.
WITH ALL THAT'S HAPPENED,
NOW YOU HAVE
A REASON TO FIGHT, TOO.
Regene:
RIBBONS. YOU HAVE A GUEST.
THE AUTONOMOUS PEACEKEEPING
FORCE ENCOUNTERED A NEW GUNDAM.
WHETHER OR NOT THE GUNDAM
BELONGS TO CELESTIAL BEING
IS STILL UNCLEAR.
GUN... DAM.
I SEE.
I'M GLAD
THEY'VE COME OUT AGAIN.
I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D BE SO HAPPY
TO BE BORN
UNDER THE SIGN OF VIRGO.
I AM FROM
THE FEDERATION MILITARY
AUTONOMOUS PEACEKEEPING FORCE,
AND I AM HERE FOR
LIEUTENANT SOMA PERIES.
I AM LIEUTENANT
ANDREI SMIRNOV
OF THE FIFTH MOBILE SUIT
COMPANY.
A‐ANDREI?
WHEN'D YOU JOIN THE A‐LAWS?
I AM NOT OBLIGATED TO ANSWER
THAT QUESTION, FATHER.
SORRY,
COLONEL SERGEI SMIRNOV.
F‐FATHER?
♪
WHY DIDN'T YOU SHOOT
SETSUNA DEAD?
KILLING SOMEONE WOULD MAKE ME
THE SAME AS YOU GUYS.
THAT'S THE
LAST THING I WANT.
Tieria:
YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL
TO SETSUNA.
IF HE HADN'T BROUGHT YOU
ALONG WITH US,
YOU LIKELY WOULD'VE
BEEN LABELED A MEMBER
OF THE ANTI‐FEDERATION GROUP,
KATHARON...
AND THEN EXECUTED.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS!
YOU'RE BLIND TO THE WAY
THINGS REALLY ARE.
OPEN YOUR EYES
AND LOOK AROUND!
AND SEE THE WORLD
THAT YOU'RE LIVING IN!
GUNDAM.
00 GUNDAM.
(Footsteps approaching)
HUH?
ARE YOU THE ONE
WHO CALLED ME HERE?
YOU'RE LYLE DYLANDY,
A MEMBER OF KATHARON.
YOU FROM SECURITY?!
I'VE COME
TO RECRUIT YOU.
HMM?
MY NAME IS...
SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
I'M A GUNDAM MEISTER
FROM CELESTIAL BEING.
YOU'RE FROM
CELESTIAL BEING.
AND YOU, TOO, ARE TO BECOME
A GUNDAM MEISTER.
LYLE DYLANDY.
OR...
LOCKON STRATOS.
Narrator:
THOSE WHO DESIRE DESTRUCTION
AND THOSE WHO REJECT IT.
NOW, WITH
THEIR DIFFERING THOUGHTS,
THEY GREET
THE AWAKENING OF 00.
NEXT EPISODE:
"TWIN DRIVE".
IS IT A GUNDAM
THAT ELIMINATES GUNDAMS?