(Rapid gunfire)
Soldier:
TRANSMISSION
FROM HEADQUARTERS, SIR.
WE'RE TO ABANDON LINE B
AT 0030
AND FALL BACK TO
THE FINAL DEFENSIVE LINE!
IGNORE THAT! SEND REINFORCEMENTS
TO FOURTH PLATOON.
HAVE ALL FORCES
BEGIN FALLING BACK.
BUT WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE THEM!
WE HAVE TO PROTECT
THE FINAL LINE WITH OUR LIVES.
OR ALL THE ENGINEERS
WORKING ON THE ORBITAL ELEVATOR,
AND THEIR FAMILIES,
WILL BE IN DANGER.
AS SOLDIERS, OUR MISSION IS
TO PROTECT THEM.
I KNOW THAT, BUT HOLLY IS
IN THE FOURTH PLATOON!
SHE'S A SOLDIER, TOO.
SHE'S PREPARED FOR THE WORST.
(Guns firing)
Andrei:
THEY NEVER FOUND
MY MOTHER'S BODY.
I'VE NEVER HAD A NORMAL
CONVERSATION
WITH MY FATHER SINCE THEN.
MY FATHER FOLLOWED HIS ORDERS
AND KILLED MY MOTHER.
♪
Feldt:
VISUAL SENSORS ARE DETECTING
A LARGE OBJECT
ATTACHED TO THE RING!
AS I FEARED.
THEY BUILT TWO OF THOSE
DAMNED THINGS?!
ARE THEY REALLY GONNA FIRE IT?
I HOPE NOT.
HOW CAN THEY BE ALLOWED
TO DO THIS?!
THEY'RE THINKING ABOUT ATTACKING
THE LOW ORBITAL STATION
WITH A SATELLITE WEAPON!
THERE'S NO DOUBT
THEY'RE GOING TO DO IT.
WHAT?!
THE COMMANDER IS PREPARED TO
TAKE ON EVERY SIN IMAGINABLE
IN ORDER TO REALIZE
PERMANENT PEACE.
Homer:
MEMENTO MORI.
HUMANITY NEEDS TO BE
REMINDED OF DEATH
AND APPRECIATE
HOW PRECIOUS PEACE IS.
Hercury:
ATTENTION, ALL HANDS.
GET THE CITIZENS
TO THE SURFACE QUICKER!
DON'T FORGET TO TELL THE
GROUND FORCES WHAT WE'RE DOING!
YES, SIR!
Hercury:
ALL HANDS, PREPARE TO EVACUATE!
I WAS BEING TOO NAIVE.
THE MOMENT I TOOK
THESE POOR PEOPLE HOSTAGE,
THE FEDERATION CONSIDERED THEM
DISSIDENTS.
BECAUSE THEY SIMPLY
KNOW THE TRUTH.
HMM?
Hercury:
THE FEDERATION WILL
DESTROY THIS PLACE
AND TAKE THE LIVES OF
60,000 PEOPLE
JUST TO FURTHER STRENGTHEN
THEIR POLITICAL DOMINANCE.
(Startled grunt)
IT'S UTTER MADNESS.
SINCE THE INDUSTRIAL
REVOLUTION,
HUMANITY HAS USED
ITS TECHNOLOGICAL KNOWLEDGE
FOR CONFLICT AND REPEATEDLY
RISKED ITS OWN EXTINCTION.
THOUGH GREAT LEADERS
APPEARED AT TIMES,
THEY'D REACH THE END OF
THEIR LIVES IN A FEW DECADES
AND THE WORLD ALWAYS RETURNED
TO A STATE OF CHAOS.
Regene:
THAT'S THE HISTORY OF THE WORLD,
OF HUMANITY.
HUMANITY NEVER LEARNS
ANYTHING FROM THE PAST.
AND THAT IS EXACTLY WHY
AEOLIA SCHENBERG
CREATED THE INNOVATORS.
THOSE WITH GREATER LIFESPANS,
WHO ARE NOT HUMAN,
WILL SAVE HUMANITY FROM
ANNIHILATION.
ALSO, WE ARE THE ONLY ONES
WITH THE SKILLS
FOR THE DIALOGUES TO COME.
YOU SEEM TO HAVE FORGOTTEN THAT
I WAS THE ONE WHO MADE YOU.
IN OTHER WORDS,
AS FAR AS YOU'RE CONCERNED,
I'M YOUR CREATOR.
HMPH.
THE INNOVATORS WON'T BE
GUIDING HUMANITY.
NOT AT ALL.
THAT TASK SHALL FALL TO ME.
Operator #1:
ELECTRICAL POWER AT 38%.
Operator #2:
SYSTEM IS OPERATING NORMALLY.
WE WILL COMMENCE STRAFING
THE MOMENT
IT'S FINISHED CHARGING.
SIR!
LO AND BEHOLD, EVERYONE!
OBSERVE AS SOMETHING THAT TOOK
THE KNOWLEDGE OF HUMANITY
OVER A HUNDRED YEARS TO BUILD
IS DESTROYED.
THOSE A‐LAWS SCUM HAVE
FINALLY SHOWN THEIR TRUE NATURE.
COULD THE INNOVATORS BE
ORCHESTRATING THIS
FROM BEHIND THE SCENES, TOO?
(Beeps)
HUH?
KATHARON FORCES
ARE MAKING A BREAK FOR IT!
(Gasps)
(Grunts)
THOSE BASTARDS.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THIS NOW?!
Tieria:
LOCKON, STOP!
Allelujah:
YOU'RE BEING TOO RECKLESS!
Operator:
THIS IS THE DAMAGE
THE WEAPON WOULD CAUSE
IF FIRED AT THE STATION.
WHAT?!
THIS IS...
Ian:
SEND PTOLEMY INTO SPACE?!
YOU MUST BE KIDDING!
WE CAN'T DO IT
IN OUR PRESENT CONDITION!
WE'RE TALKING
MILLIONS OF LIVES HERE!
(Door opens)
HUH?
SETSUNA?
I'LL USE THE 00.
Sumeragi:
WHAT?! BUT YOU'RE IN
NO SHAPE‐‐
THE ONLY THING
THAT HAS A CHANCE
AT STOPPING THAT SATELLITE
WEAPON IS THE 00 RAISER.
Setsuna:
BUT YOU ALREADY KNOW THAT.
THE TRANS AM RAISER.
I NEED A MISSION PLAN.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED A PILOT
FOR THE 0 RAISER.
I GUESS I COULD ASK LASSE,
BUT HE'S...
YOU WILL BE THE PILOT.
HUH?
YOU WANT ME?!
Setsuna:
60,000 LIVES ARE AT STAKE HERE.
WE'RE FIGHTING TO PROTECT THEM.
TO PROTECT PEOPLE.
(Grunts)
THE CHANCE OF SUCCESS
ISN'T VERY HIGH.
BUT I DON'T WANNA GIVE UP
WITHOUT AT LEAST TRYING.
WE'RE FIGHTING TO
PROTECT PEOPLE.
YOU'D BETTER WEAR THIS.
HUH?
DON'T LET US DOWN.
DO YOUR BEST TO SAVE LIVES.
(Grunts)
RIGHT!
Sumeragi:
WE'LL USE THE CATAPULT
TO PERFORM A TWO STAGE
ACCELERATION. UNDERSTAND?
Setsuna:
ROGER!
Saji: YEAH, ROGER THAT!
I'M REALLY FIGHTING A MACHINE.
I'M NOT FIGHTING PEOPLE.
Feldt:
OPENING PTOLEMY'S
FIRST AND THIRD HATCHES.
TRANSFERRING LAUNCH TIMING
TO THE TWO MACHINES.
SETSUNA F. SEIEI,
LAUNCHING!
SAJI CROSSROAD,
I'M TAKING OFF!
(Straining)
Setsuna:
COMMENCE DOCKING!
0 RAISER, DOCKING MODE!
Hercury:
ALL THE CIVILIANS AND THE
SOLDIERS ARE ON THEIR WAY DOWN.
YOU SHOULD LEAVE TOO.
(Grunts)
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I AM THE COMMANDER
OF THIS OPERATION.
I WILL STAY AND SEE IT THROUGH
TO THE END.
WHATEVER HAPPENS AFTER THIS,
PLEASE MAKE SURE FUTURE
GENERATIONS KNOW THE TRUTH.
THIS ISN'T THE RIGHT WAY TO
ATONE FOR YOUR SINS!
YOU ARE A SOLDIER
AND A SOLDIER MUST ALWAYS
PROTECT THE CITIZENS!
SAVE AS MANY PEOPLE AS YOU CAN,
THEN YOU CAN DIE.
(Grunts)
(Beeps)
HMM?
Sergei:
THEY'RE PREPARING TO FIRE?
LET'S GO!
(Grunts)
(Whirring)
Operator:
POWER SUPPLY AT 93%!
ENEMY APPROACHING, SIR!
HAVE THE EMPRUSS
LAUNCH AT ONCE.
YES, SIR!
SETSUNA.
PREPARING TO RELEASE
ALL COMPRESSED PARTICLES!
Setsuna:
ACTIVATE THE RAISER SYSTEM!
UH... UNDERSTOOD!
AN ENEMY!
I CAN'T LET YOU DO THAT, GUNDAM!
(Screaming)
S‐SAJI!
Saji:
THE SYSTEM!
NOW I'LL AVENGE...
BRING'S DEATH!
TRANS AM RAISER!
(Gasps)
Operator:
WE'RE AT FULL POWER, SIR.
COMMENCE STRAFING.
COMMENCING
STRAFING!
INCOMING HIGH ENERGY
BLAST, SIR!
A WHAT?
(Sighs)
IT MISSED US!
THE BEAM IS MOVING, SIR!
HUH?
Goodman:
IT'S DOING WHAT?!
THAT MEANS WE'RE NOT
BEING SHOT AT!
IT'S A BEAM SABER!
(Aggressive yelling)
(Gasps)
WE DID IT!
Setsuna:
IT WASN'T ENOUGH!
HUH?
NO.
DON'T DO IT.
DON'T DO IT!
(Whirring)
SIR!
THE PILLAR UNDER
THE LOW ORBITAL STATION
IS STARTING TO AUTO‐PURGE!
CHECK THE AUTO‐BALANCERS!
Operator:
CONFIRMED!
THE ANCHORS ARE RELEASING!
HUH? THE PILLAR'S SHELL
IS CRACKING!
(Grunts)
HURRY UP!
(Gasps)
Feldt:
THE LASER STRUCK THE PILLAR!
THE PILLAR'S EXTERNAL SHELL IS
STARTING TO AUTO‐PURGE!
FRAGMENTS ENTERING FROM
ABOVE THE STRATOSPHERE
WILL BURN UP
DUE TO ATMOSPHERIC HEATING,
BUT FRAGMENTS FROM
THE SECTIONS BELOW
WILL HIT THE EARTH.
(Screaming)
IT'S MY FAULT.
Sergei:
PULL IT TOGETHER!
RIGHT NOW, THINK ABOUT HOW
WE CAN PREVENT ANY MORE DAMAGE!
WHAT'S THAT?
THEY REALLY DID IT.
IT'S THE ORBITAL ELEVATOR!
Tieria:
IT'S COLLAPSING!
MISS SUMERAGI.
TO ALL UNITS
IN THIS AIRSPACE.
WHAT'S THIS?
I'M TRANSMITTING DATA
VIA A VISUAL COMLINK.
PLEASE DESTROY
THE PILLAR FRAGMENTS
THAT WILL BE ENTERING
THE AIR SPACES I'VE INDICATED.
BELOW THEM ARE
DENSELY POPULATED AREAS.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?!
UNLESS WE WORK TOGETHER
AND DO OUR BEST,
TENS OF MILLIONS
OF LIVES WILL BE LOST.
I'M BEGGING YOU,
SAVE THOSE PEOPLE'S LIVES.
COMPRESSED PARTICLES,
RELEASING!
(Panicked screaming)
HARO!
DEPLOYING SHIELD BITS!
(Grunts)
(Stunned gasps)
THERE ARE JUST TOO MANY OF THEM!
DAMN IT!
(Gasps)
THAT'S...
Allelujah:
MARIE!
THIS DOESN'T COUNT AS A BATTLE!
IT'S TO SAVE LIVES!
HMM.
DAMN IT.
IF THIS KEEPS UP...
IT GOT PAST!
(Gasps)
I THINK THAT'S...
KATHARON!
(Grunts)
(Gasps)
UNITS FROM THE COUP D'ETAT?
THIS IS A HELL OF A MESS!
WHAT'S THIS?!
IT'S THE REGULAR ARMY!
(Tense grunt)
(Gasps)
IT LOOKS LIKE
THE URBAN AREAS
ARE GONNA BE SPARED
ANY DIRECT HITS!
(Relieved sigh)
MY THANKS TO ALL.
IN TIMES LIKE THIS,
I GUESS EVERYBODY
COMES TOGETHER AS ONE.
THAT'S WHAT I CALL IRONY.
(Chuckles)
BUT IT ISN'T BAD!
HMM.
(Gasps)
Feldt:
MOBILE SUIT TEAMS ARE
APPROACHING US FROM PORTSIDE!
IT'S A‐LAWS!
THEY WERE WAITING FOR
THIS OPPORTUNITY!
LET'S CALL BACK
MR. ERDE AND THE OTHERS!
WE'LL KEEP ON LIKE THIS!
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
HMM.
(Kati thinking)
IF SHE IS THEIR COMMANDER,
I KNOW WHAT SHE'LL DO.
HMM?
I KNOW WE HAVE OUR ORDERS,
BUT STILL...
I WILL NOT ABANDON
PEOPLE TO THEIR FATE!
I'M GONNA BE
DIFFERENT FROM MY FATHER!
(Grunts)
(Beeps)
HUH?
THAT MACHINE!
MARIE!
Andrei:
WHAT? YOU'RE SAYING
YOU SAW MACHINES
COME OUT OF THE PILLAR?
YES.
THEY COULD BE
THE LEADERS OF THE REBELLION.
FOLLOW ME.
ROGER!
Sergei:
THANK YOU FOR YOUR HELP.
Peries:
I THOUGHT IT WAS YOU,
COLONEL SMIRNOV!
THAT YOU, PERIES?
WHY ARE YOU IN A MOBILE SUIT?
Peries:
INCOMING!
HUH?
A‐LAWS!
I KNOW THAT VOICE.
COLONEL HERCURY?!
Hercury:
HUH? ANDREI!
WHAT THE HELL?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?!
Louise:
LIEUTENANT!
THAT'S A HUGE FRAGMENT!
WHAT?
DAMN IT, IT DIDN'T FULLY
AUTO‐PURGE!
IF THAT THING HITS...
A GUNDAM!
Tieria:
TRANS AM!
GN BAZOOKA!
FIRING HYPER‐BURST MODE!
IT DIDN'T WORK!
LOCKON!
ALLELUJAH!
TRANS AM TIME!
STARTING TRANS AM!
THAT'S THE ORBITAL ELEVATOR.
AFTER THIS,
WHAT'S THE WORLD
GONNA BE LIKE?
IF ONLY EVERYONE
COULD HEAR OUR SONG.
(Car horn blaring)
(Murmuring)
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
(Beeps)
HMM?
I SEE YOU MADE IT,
HERCURY.
UNBELIEVABLE.
WHAT HAPPENED HERE WAS JUST...
THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT CAN NEVER BE TAKEN BACK.
HUH?
HERCURY!
(Gasps)
Andrei:
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT!
YOU'RE THE ONES
WHO CAUSED THIS CATASTROPHE!
YOU BASTARD!
THAT VOICE!
ANDREI!
FATHER.
DON'T TELL ME YOU WERE
FIGHTING WITH THE REBELS!
BUT WHY?
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?!
J‐JUST WAIT!
(Grunts)
YOU KILLED MOTHER FOR THE SAKE
OF YOUR PRECIOUS ORDERS,
AND YET NOW YOU'RE SUPPORTING
THE COUP D'ÉTAT?!
ANDREI, JUST WAIT A MINUTE!
YOU'RE A DISGRACE AS A SOLDIER!
NO, COLONEL SMIRNOV!
(Gasps)
YOU'RE NOT GETTING AWAY,
CELESTIAL BEING!
Saji:
LOUISE!
I'M COMING, COLONEL!
THIS IS REVENGE!
ANDREI.
FOR MOTHER!
♪
Holly:
DARLING?
Sergei:
HMM?
Holly:
IF SOMETHING SHOULD HAPPEN TO ME
DURING THE NEXT MISSION,
PLEASE, TAKE CARE OF ANDREI.
Sergei:
HEY, COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
BUT, DON'T WORRY.
(Door opens)
HUH?
(Groaning)
ANDREI, I'M...
SO SORRY.
(Gasps)
YOU HAD CLOSED
YOUR HEART OFF.
I DIDN'T KNOW
HOW TO APPROACH YOU.
I DIDN'T TRY AS MUCH AS
I SHOULD'VE.
Andrei:
WHY ARE YOU
SAYING THIS NOW?!
(Groans)
Sergei:
GET... GET AWAY FROM ME!
(Gasping in pain)
(Groaning)
HOLLY.
FORGIVE ME.
(Gasps)
COLONEL.
HUH?
THAT WAS COLONEL SMIRNOV.
(Sobs)
(Screaming)
COLONEL!
Narrator:
FOUR MONTHS SINCE THE COLLAPSE
OF THE ORBITAL ELEVATOR.
AS THE WORLD UNDERGOES
A DRAMATIC CHANGE,
DO THE PEOPLE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO BE TOSSED TO AND FRO?
NEXT EPISODE:
"ENTANGLED YEARNINGS".
IN THE MIDST OF BATTLE,
SOMEBODY CRIES OUT.