Hercury:
THIS IS A MESSAGE
FOR ALL CITIZENS HERE.
I AM COLONEL PANG HERCURY,
OF THE EARTH SPHERE
FEDERATION FORCES,
INFORMATION OPERATIONS CENTER.
MY COMRADES AND I HAVE TAKEN
CONTROL OF THIS STATION.
WE ARE NOW IN CONTROL OF
THE GARRISON FORCES,
THE LIFE SUPPORT SYSTEM,
THE LINEAR TRAINS
AND THE SOLAR
POWER GENERATION SYSTEM.
WE HAVE BUT ONE OBJECTIVE.
WE WANT TO INFORM THE WORLD OF
THE BRUTALITY OF THE A‐LAWS,
THE FEDERATION GOVERNMENT'S
AUTONOMOUS PEACEKEEPING FORCE,
SO THE PUBLIC CAN DECIDE
WHETHER THEY ARE TRULY
IN THE RIGHT.
ARE YOU AWARE
THAT UNDER THE GUISE
OF ELIMINATING
ANTI‐GOVERNMENT FORCES,
THEY HAVE MASSACRED MILLIONS
OF PEOPLE IN COLD BLOOD?
DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY INNOCENT
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN KILLED
IN THEIR BID TO
REORGANIZE THE MIDDLE EAST?
IT'S ALL TRUE. YOU HAVE BEEN
HANDED A FALSE PEACE
BY THE FEDERATION'S
INFORMATION CONTROL.
AND WITHOUT EVEN KNOWING IT,
YOU HAVE ALL BEEN
LIVING IN A DICTATORSHIP.
WHILE WE ARE DISCLOSING THESE
FACTS TO THE WORLD,
I'M AFRAID THAT YOUR
LIVES WILL BE IN OUR HANDS.
GO AHEAD AND DESPISE ME
IF YOU WISH.
BUT LET ME MAKE
SOMETHING PERFECTLY CLEAR.
AS SOLDIERS WE'RE SWORN
TO PROTECT
THE INTERESTS
OF THE FEDERATION'S CITIZENS.
AND THAT IS WHY,
CORRECTING THE MISTAKES
OF A MISGUIDED GOVERNMENT
AND MILITARY
IS ALSO THE SWORN
DUTY OF A SOLDIER!
♪
Spokesperson:
THE FEDERATION ASSEMBLY
HAS RECEIVED
A CLAIM OF RESPONSIBILITY
AND A LIST OF DEMANDS
FROM THE ANTI‐GOVERNMENT
FORCES THAT TOOK CONTROL OF
THE AFRICA TOWER'S
LOW ORBITAL STATION.
IN EXCHANGE FOR THE RELEASE
OF THE CITIZENS IN THE STATION,
THEY DEMAND THE DISSOLUTION OF
THE FEDERATION ASSEMBLY,
THE RELEASE
OF FORTY‐FIVE THOUSAND
ANTI‐GOVERNMENT ACTIVISTS,
AND ONE HUNDRED BILLION DOLL‐‐
BUT THE FEDERATION GOVERNMENT
WILL NOT SUBMIT
TO THESE DEMANDS NOR
WILL IT YIELD TO TERRORISM.
THE GOVERNMENT
HAS ALREADY DISPATCHED
THE AUTONOMOUS
PEACEKEEPING FORCE
TO THE SCENE TO BRING
A SWIFT CONCLUSION.
(TV beeps off)
INFORMATION CONTROL...
THIS IS JUST MORE LIES.
AGAINST THEIR POWERFUL SYSTEM...
WHAT CAN YOU POSSIBLY
ACCOMPLISH, HERCURY?
Hercury:
THE SOLAR POWER GENERATION
SYSTEM WE'RE CREATING
WITH THE ORBITAL ELEVATORS
IS THE HOPE THAT IS GOING TO
LEAD HUMANITY INTO THE FUTURE.
SO MANY OF
THE WORLD'S CONFLICTS
ARE THE RESULT OF WIDESPREAD
ENERGY SHORTAGES.
IF WE CAN SOLVE
THE ENERGY CRISIS,
THEN WE CAN TURN OUR EFFORTS
TO DEALING WITH
THE FOOD AND
ENVIRONMENTAL PROBLEMS.
THAT'S TRUE, BUT THE NATIONAL
BLOCS THAT CONTROL
THE ORBITAL ELEVATORS SEEM
TO BE EXPANDING THEIR MILITARIES
IN THE NAME OF DEFENSE.
EVENTUALLY IT'S GOING TO LEAD
TO INCREASED TENSION
BETWEEN THESE
STRENGTHENED NATIONAL BLOCS.
IN OTHER WORDS,
ISN'T THIS JUST GOING TO BRING
ABOUT ANOTHER COLD WAR?
LOOK, EVEN IF
IT DOES COME TO THAT
WITH A RESPONSIBLE CITIZENRY,
A COMPETENT GOVERNMENT
AND A PROPERLY FUNCTIONING
MILITARY LIKE OURS
TO ACT AS A DETERRENT
AGAINST CONFLICT...
THE PATH WILL OPEN!
WE CAN ALLEVIATE
THE TENSION,
AND WORK TOGETHER
TO REACH A DEEPER
UNDERSTANDING.
AND THEN GRADUALLY,
THE WORLD WILL BECOME UNITED.
(Beeping)
HUH?
COMMANDER KIM!
COLONEL, I HAVE A SECRET MISSION
I WANT TO ENTRUST TO YOU.
A SECRET MISSION?
Homer:
WHAT'S THE SITUATION?
SIR, THE REGULAR FORCES
HAVE SURROUNDED
THE LOW ORBITAL STATION.
I'VE SENT OUT A DISPATCH
ORDERING THE ELITE A‐LAWS FORCES
ON THE SURFACE
TO HEAD TO THE SITE.
A COUP D'ÉTAT
AMONG THE REGULAR FORCES.
IF THIS INFORMATION GETS OUT TO
THE GENERAL PUBLIC,
IT COULD EASILY CAUSE
ANTI‐GOVERNMENT ACTIVITY
TO SPREAD.
THE WORK CONNECTING EVERYTHING
TO THE ORBITAL RING
WILL BE COMPLETED SHORTLY, SIR.
I'M GOING INTO SPACE TO TAKE
PERSONAL COMMAND.
VERY GOOD. CARRY ON THEN.
Nena:
LETTING THE REBELS JUST
WALTZ IN THERE
AND DO WHATEVER THEY WANT.
SOMETIMES I WONDER
WHAT THOSE INNOVATORS
ARE THINKING, MY MISTRESS.
ONLY THEY KNOW WHAT
THEIR PLANS ARE.
DO YOU SUPPOSE
THIS GROUP'S COUP D'ÉTAT
WILL CHANGE THE WORLD?
WHO KNOWS?
IT COULD BE THE BEGINNING OF
THE END OF EVERYTHING.
AND IS THAT WHAT YOU TRULY
DESIRE, MY MISTRESS?
WE ARE COMPLETELY SURROUNDED,
BOTH UP HERE AND
ON THE GROUND, COLONEL.
DON'T WORRY.
IT'S JUST AS WE PLANNED.
ANY NEWS FROM KATHARON?
THEY SAY A FAIR NUMBER OF
THEIR MOBILE SUITS
ARE ALREADY ON
THEIR WAY HERE, SIR.
ALL THAT'S LEFT IS TO SEE WHAT
ACTION CELESTIAL BEING TAKES.
THE AFRICA TOWER OCCUPIED BY
A COUP D'ÉTAT FORCE.
IT'S EXACTLY WHAT
KATHARON TOLD US ABOUT.
THIS MUST BE
WHY THE A‐LAWS
SUDDENLY WITHDREW FROM
THE BATTLE.
WELL, WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO
ABOUT IT, MISS SUMERAGI?
Lyle:
OBVIOUSLY, WE'RE GOING
TO HELP THEM, RIGHT?
THE INNOVATORS HAVE COMPLETE
CONTROL OF VEDA.
SO THEN HOW DID
THEY FAIL TO NOTICE
THE PLANNING OF THIS INCIDENT?
ARE YOU SAYING THEY
PREDICTED THE COUP D'ÉTAT,
BUT STILL LET
IT GO AHEAD?
IT IS A POSSIBILITY.
BUT NOW THAT THE A‐LAWS
ARE BECOMING INVOLVED,
WE CAN'T JUST SIT
BACK HERE
AND WATCH
WHAT HAPPENS.
ALSO, THE REAL MASTERMINDS
BEHIND THE A‐LAWS
ARE THE INNOVATORS.
REGARDLESS OF WHATEVER THEY'RE
PLANNING TO DO
WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO ACTUALLY GO THERE
AND FIND OUT FOR OURSELVES.
FURTHERMORE,
ONCE SETSUNA FINDS OUT
A COUP D'ÉTAT'S
TAKEN PLACE...
HE'D HEAD THERE!
YEAH!
HE SURE WOULD!
IAN, CAN YOU GET THE WEAPONS
CONTROL SYSTEM
WORKING BEFORE WE
REACH THE AFRICA TOWER?
I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE, DO I?
Operator:
A‐LAWS MOBILE SUIT TEAMS
HAVE LAUNCHED.
WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH
THAT EXTRA EQUIPMENT?
DON'T LOOK AT ME,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY HAVE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THE A‐LAWS AND THEIR SECRETS.
WE'RE TO REMAIN ON STANDBY AT
OUR CURRENT POSITION.
COLONEL, WE'RE DETECTING
A‐LAWS MOBILE SUIT TEAMS.
DON'T INTERCEPT THEM.
THE WORLD IS WATCHING.
MOBILE SUIT TEAMS
ARE RELEASING CONTAINERS.
(Scoff)
THE INFAMOUS AUTOMATONS.
(Clunk)
(Whizz)
(Boom)
SIR, THEY'RE THROUGH
THE BULKHEAD WALLS!
SWITCH THE DEFENSES
TO MODE "S" TO REPEL THEM,
JUST LIKE WE PLANNED.
(Blasts)
(Beep)
43 PERCENT OF THE AUTOMATONS
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED, SIR.
JUST A SCOUTING PARTY,
PERHAPS?
I'M NOT SO SURE.
COLONEL, DETECTING KATHARON
FORCES APPROACHING THE PILLAR.
Hercury:
IS THE FEDERATION
INTERCEPTING THEM?
NEGATIVE, SIR.
KATHARON UNITS HAVE ENTERED
THE PILLAR'S LAUNCH BAY.
THAT MEANS THEY'VE JOINED UP
WITH OUR GROUND FORCES, SIR.
THE A‐LAWS MUST HAVE BEEN
DEPLOYED ON THE SURFACE AS WELL.
YET, THEY'VE CHOSEN
NOT TO ATTACK.
Soldier:
COLONEL!
WHAT IS IT NOW?
A MACHINE HAS ENTERED
THE PILLAR AT SECTOR DH42, SIR.
AND IT'S ASCENDING.
IS IT A‐LAWS?
IT'S ON THE SCREEN, SIR.
(Gasp)
WHY THAT'S...
THAT'S A TIEREN TAOZI.
SEND SOME MOBILE SUITS
TO ESCORT IT.
COLONEL?
I GUESS IT'S THE LEAST
WE CAN DO.
Hercury:
A GOOD FRIEND IS IN
THAT MACHINE.
AS YOU INSTRUCTED, I'VE SENT
COLONEL SMIRNOV
FROM OUR FORCES
AS A SECRET MESSENGER.
Homer:
YOUR COOPERATION
IS APPRECIATED.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU COULD
ASSIGN ME THE RANK OF GENERAL
WHEN I TRANSFER OVER TO
THE A‐LAWS, SIR.
IT'S A PROMISE.
GOODBYE.
(Sigh)
EVENTUALLY,
EVEN THE REGULAR ARMY
WILL BE ABSORBED BY
THE A‐LAWS.
IS THIS ANOTHER
SIGN OF THE TIMES?
Kati:
REMAIN AT SEA ON STANDBY?
BUT WHY?
WHY WON'T THEY MOBILIZE
THE FORCES I HAVE HERE?!
LOOKS LIKE WE WON'T
BE NEEDED OUT THERE.
THIS IS A BIG OPERATION.
WHY DOES RIBBONS
KEEP DOING THESE THINGS?
YOU LOOK IRRITATED.
STILL WAITING TO AVENGE BRING?
WHAT WAS THAT?
(Laughing)
WE CAN TELL, YOU KNOW!
WE'RE ALL THE SAME,
AFTER ALL!
Louise:
YOU KNOW THE LEADER
OF THE REBELS?
HE'S ONE OF MY FATHER'S
CLOSEST FRIENDS.
WHEN I WAS A CHILD, HE WOULD
TELL ME ABOUT THE MILITARY.
ABOUT THE IDEALS
A REAL ARMY SHOULD HAVE.
AND NOW HE'S BECOME A REBEL,
SITTING UP IN A STATION
WITH SIXTY THOUSAND
HOSTAGES AROUND HIM.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT THE
REASONS FOR THE REBELLION ARE.
AS MEMBERS OF THE A‐LAWS,
OUR MISSION IS TO
STRIKE DOWN
ALL ANTI‐GOVERNMENT
FORCES
TO RESTORE
PEACE AND ORDER AGAIN.
YES, OF COURSE IT IS,
WARRANT OFFICER.
HUH?
SO IT'S TRUE THEN,
I SEE YOU'VE ALREADY ENROLLED
IN THE MILITARY ACADEMY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR
PUTTING IN A GOOD WORD
FOR ME WITH
THE HIGHER‐UPS, SIR.
I DIDN'T WANT TO RELY ON
MY FATHER'S ASSISTANCE.
SO, ARE YOU JOINING
THE MILITARY AS A WAY
TO GET BACK AT YOUR FATHER?
HMM.
DON'T RESENT YOUR
FATHER TOO MUCH.
THAT WAS TRULY
AN UNFORTUNATE ACCIDENT.
DON'T DISMISS WHAT HAPPENED
BY CALLING IT
SOMETHING ELSE, SIR!
MY FATHER ALLOWED MY MOTHER
TO DIE.
AND YOU'RE
THE SAME AS HIM!
(Sigh)
I'M NOT GOING TO LIVE MY LIFE
LIKE MY FATHER DID!
I'VE CHOSEN THE PATH
OF A SOLDIER
TO PROVE THAT
THERE'S ANOTHER WAY!
DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE THAT
THAT KIND OF ATTITUDE
WOULD HAVE MADE HOLLY HAPPY?
YES, I DO.
BECAUSE MY MOTHER
DESIRED PEACE
MORE THAN ANYONE ELSE.
Andrei:
COLONEL...
HALFHEARTED DETERMINATION WILL
NOT BRING ABOUT PEACE.
WHY CAN'T YOU UNDERSTAND
THAT THE POWER OF THE A‐LAWS
IS NECESSARY IN
TODAY'S WORLD?
SO YOU CAME AFTER ALL, SERGEI.
HERCURY.
(Computers beeping)
HERCURY, I'M HERE TO
GIVE YOU A SECRET MESSAGE
FROM THE EARTH SPHERE
FEDERATION FORCES.
THE FEDERATION GOVERNMENT
WILL NEVER SUBMIT
TO THE DEMANDS
YOU'VE MADE.
WE ADVISE YOU TO
SURRENDER IMMEDIATELY.
(Chuckle)
YOU'RE TELLING ME YOU
CAME ALL THE WAY UP HERE
JUST TO TELL ME
SUCH A TRIFLE?
THE FEDERATION
GOVERNMENT'S INFORMATION
CONTROL SYSTEM IS
ABSOLUTE.
THERE'S NO WAY YOUR MESSAGE IS
GOING TO REACH THE WORLD.
WHY HAVE YOU TAKEN
INNOCENT CITIZENS HOSTAGE?
THEY ARE NOT
INNOCENT AT ALL.
Hercury:
CONTENT WITH THEIR WEALTH,
THEY ACCEPT THE ASSEMBLY'S
POLICIES WITHOUT QUESTION.
THEY ARE ONE
OF THE MAIN REASONS
FOR THE GOVERNMENT'S CORRUPTION.
IT'S THE FOLLY OF THESE
CITIZENS THAT ALLOWED
THE RISE OF AN ORGANIZATION
LIKE THE A‐LAWS.
WE MUST OPEN THEIR EYES AND
SHOW THEM THE TRUTH.
EVEN IF THE LESSON
IS ACCOMPANIED BY PAIN.
ISN'T THE MILITARY SUPPOSED TO
PROTECT THE INTERESTS
AND SAFETY OF THE PEOPLE?
THAT IS PRECISELY WHY
WE'RE DOING THIS!
JUST SURRENDER!
IF YOU DO IT NOW,
THERE'S A CHANCE YOU CAN STILL
SAVE THE LIVES OF YOUR MEN!
THE A‐LAWS WON'T BE
THAT FORGIVING.
(Grunt)
HERCURY...
Hercury:
THIS MEETING IS OVER.
HUH?
RETURN TO THE SURFACE
AND CONVEY MY RESPONSE
TO HEADQUARTERS.
WE ARE NOT LEAVING HERE,
AND WE WILL FIGHT TO
THE LAST MAN TO HOLD ONTO IT.
TAKE HIM AWAY.
SIR!
HUH? ARGH.
NO, I'M STAYING RIGHT HERE!
WHAT WAS THAT?
DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE
I CAME HERE
ONLY BECAUSE
I WAS ORDERED TO?
I DON'T WANT TO
LOSE ANOTHER‐‐
COLONEL!
HMM?
NEW AUTOMATONS HAVE
BROKEN THROUGH!
THEY'RE HEADING FOR
THE GRAVITY BLOCK, SIR!
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
(Grunting)
Hercury:
CLOSE THE BULKHEAD WALLS
LIKE WE PLANNED!
HAVE FIRST INFANTRY UNIT
SECURE THE ROUTE
AND GUIDE THE CITIZENS
ONTO THE TRAINS!
SECOND INFANTRY UNIT
WILL INTERCEPT THE AUTOMATONS!
Soldier:
YES, SIR!
HERCURY...
ARE YOU...
Woman:
THIS IS SO CRAZY.
(Curious chatter)
(Guns blasting)
(People screaming)
(Clank)
Soldier:
THE AUTOMATONS ARE ATTACKING
THE CITIZENS TOO, SIR!
(Yell)
(Shocked scream)
(Blasts)
SIR, WE HAVE
CIVILIAN CASUALTIES!
CIVILIANS?
THEY'VE PROGRAMMED
THE AUTOMATONS FOR KILL MODE?
DO YOU SEE, SERGEI?
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS WITH
A MISGUIDED GOVERNMENT
AND MILITARY!
HMM.
Soldier #1:
ESCAPE ROUTE SECURED!
Soldier #2:
WE'RE PUTTING THE CITIZENS
ON BOARD THE TRAINS.
(Panicked yelling)
Shirin:
OUR MOBILE SUIT TEAMS
HAVE LINKED UP
WITH THE COUP D'ÉTAT FORCES.
IF WE CAN USE THIS
TO INFORM THE WORLD
ABOUT THE FEDERATION'S
MISGOVERNMENT
AND THE A‐LAWS' ATROCITIES,
THEN JUST MAYBE...
BUT REMEMBER,
WE'RE THE ONES REBELLING
AGAINST THE STATUS
QUO HERE.
I WONDER IF THE WORLD
WILL ACCEPT OUR VERSION
AS THE REAL ONE.
(Door opens)
HUH?
THE FEDERATION'S MAKING
AN OFFICIAL ANNOUNCEMENT!
Klaus:
ARE THEY FINALLY
GOING TO NEGOTIATE?
Soldier:
FIRST LINEAR TRAIN HAS
DEPARTED, SIR.
THE SECOND ONE WILL LEAVE
IN FIVE MINUTES.
YOU WERE PLANNING TO RELEASE THE
CITIZENS FROM THE VERY START.
THEN WHAT'S THE POINT OF THIS?
LIKE I TOLD YOU...
I'M GOING TO
OPEN THE CITIZEN'S EYES
BY HAVING THEM WITNESS
THE ATROCITIES
OF THE FEDERATION
GOVERNMENT'S A‐LAWS.
EVEN IF IT'S ACCOMPANIED
BY PAIN.
(Shots blasting)
(Men grunting in pain)
THAT PAIN
WILL LEAD TO DOUBTS
ABOUT THE FEDERATION
GOVERNMENT...
AND THEN THE DOUBTS WILL
BEGIN TO GROW.
THE GOVERNMENT AND
THE MILITARY MUST HAVE
RESPONSIBLE CITIZENS
IN ORDER TO FUNCTION PROPERLY.
I WILL HAPPILY
SACRIFICE MYSELF
IF THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES
TO OPEN THEIR EYES.
HERCURY...
COLONEL!
THE FEDERATION'S
ANNOUNCEMENT!
YES,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
THESE IMAGES WERE RECORDED BY
UNMANNED RECONNAISSANCE
DRONES DEPLOYED BY THE
AUTONOMOUS PEACEKEEPING FORCE
INSIDE THE AFRICA TOWER.
HMM?
(Yell)
(Shocked scream)
(Shots blast)
BUT‐BUT THESE ARE...
Spokesperson:
THE ANTI‐GOVERNMENT FORCES
HAVE BEGUN KILLING
THE CITIZENS IN THE STATION.
THE ASSEMBLY IS CURRENTLY
CONSIDERING A FORCED ENTRY
BY THE AUTONOMOUS
PEACEKEEPING‐‐
OH MAN, WHAT THE HELL'S UP
WITH THOSE IMAGES?!
FALSE INFORMATION TO
AROUSE THE PEOPLE'S ANGER.
THE FEDERATION
IS A MASTER AT THIS.
THERE WILL NEVER BE A PERMANENT
PEACE AS LONG
AS THEY RESORT TO
SUCH DECEITFUL METHODS!
THAT IS WHY WE MUST
DO EVERYTHING IN OUR POWER
TO BRING ABOUT THE END OF
THE FEDERATION!
Hercury:
NO MATTER WHAT
DECEPTIONS THEY USE,
THE TRUTH WILL BE
OUT SOON ENOUGH.
THAT IS WHY I ORDERED
THE CITIZENS
TO BE SENT TO THE SURFACE.
I CAN'T IMAGINE THIS WHOLE
SCHEME OF YOURS
IS OUTSIDE THE
FEDERATION'S EXPECTATIONS.
EVEN SO, THEY'LL NEVER
BE ABLE TO SILENCE
SIXTY THOUSAND EYEWITNESSES.
ALSO, FRIENDLY FORCES AND
KATHARON ARE ON THE GROUND.
THEY'RE SPREADING
THIS FALSE INFORMATION
TO GAIN THE PUBLIC'S SUPPORT.
GIVING THEM AN EXCUSE TO
BEGIN THEIR ATTACK.
Sergei:
YOU KNOW,
THE A‐LAWS MUST HAVE A PLAN.
(Zoom)
(Alert beep)
HUH?
THIS MOBILE SUIT
IS LIKE...
BUT IT'S NOT A FLAG!
(Grunt)
(Yelling)
Graham:
I KNEW I COULD COUNT ON
MEETING YOU HERE...
ONCE YOU HEARD
ABOUT THE AFRICA TOWER!
BACK OFF!
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO
MESS AROUND WITH YOU RIGHT NOW!
(Setsuna grunts)
HOW CAN YOU BE SO
CRUEL TO ME?
WELL, HERE'S SOMETHING
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO IGNORE.
OBSERVE CAREFULLY NOW.
THIS IS THE SECRET OF
THE MASURAO MY FRIEND CREATED!
BUT‐BUT THAT'S...
TRANS AM!
(Clash)
(Clang)
(Setsuna yells)
(Clanging)
(Pained grunt)
YOU'RE WIDE OPEN!
(Tense sigh)
(Groaning)
Graham:
FORGIVE ME
FOR DESTROYING YOU!
(Sigh)
(Grunt)
(Growl)
(Smash)
(Clash)
(Yelling)
I LIVE FOR
THE SAKE OF COMBAT!
A LIFE FOR FIGHTING!
AGAINST GUNDAMS!
I'M THE SAME!
AND I'LL SURPASS THE GUNDAMS!
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON...
BUT NOW I KNOW THAT....
I EXIST!
I'M DIFFERENT THAN I USED TO BE!
Sumeragi:
SETSUNA!
HUH?
(Gasp)
(Shots blasting)
WE'RE BEING INTERRUPTED!
MY PARTICLES ARE LOW.
LISTEN CAREFULLY,
YOUNG MAN!
DON'T FORGET ME!
Allelujah:
SETSUNA!
STILL ALIVE AND KICKING.
WHAT A GUY.
THAT'S GOOD NEWS!
Setsuna: (Groaning)
G‐GUYS...
SETSUNA?!
Setsuna:
IS EVERYONE ALL RIGHT?
SETSUNA,
WHAT'S WRONG?
Setsuna:
(Fainting sigh)
Allelujah:
SETSUNA!
Lyle:
Lockon:
SETSUNA.
(Grunt)
YOU CHOULD CHANGE.
I COULDN'T, SO YOU'LL
HAVE TO DO IT FOR ME.
I HEAR YOU... LOCKON.
I'LL CHANGE RIGHT HERE.
I'M GOING
TO REFORM MYSELF.
♪
THE ARMY'S LIFTING
ITS SIEGE.
IT'S WHAT?
WHAT'S THE MEANING
OF THIS?
OUR FORCES ARE
ASSEMBLING IN TWO PLACES.
MAYBE THEY DON'T INTEND TO
LAUNCH AN ATTACK
UNTIL THE HOSTAGES
ARE RELEASED.
HMM.
Sumeragi:
NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
THIS BATTLE FORMATION
IS CONCEALING
A MUCH BIGGER MEANING.
FELDT, SHOW THE WIND
SPEED DATA WITHIN
ONE THOUSAND KILOMETERS
OF THE TOWER.
BUT‐BUT WHAT FOR?
JUST HURRY!
UH! THAT MEANS...
THEY'RE DEPLOYING
THEIR FORCES
LIKE THEY'RE PREPARING FOR
FALLING DEBRIS.
IT CAN'T BE!
(Grunt)
THAT MEANS...THEY HAVE ANOTHER
ONE OF THOSE THINGS.
Operator #1:
MEMENTO MORI, BEGINNING
STRAFING PREPARATIONS.
Operator #2:
COMMENCING
ELECTRICAL POWER FLOW.
Operator #3:
ELECTRICAL POWER FLOW
HAS STARTED.
Operator #4:
0187 UNTIL FULLY CHARGED.
SETTING 6800 AS MAXIMUM
OUTPUT VALUE.
THE REBEL FORCES AND KATHARON.
AND THEN CELESTIAL BEING
WILL SHOW UP.
WHEN ALL OF YOU
ARE GATHERED TOGETHER
YOU WILL FEEL THE FORCE
OF GOD'S THUNDER!
Narrator:
A FLASH AND DESTRUCTION.
DESPAIR AND AGONY.
IN THE MIDST OF
A BATTLE WHERE LIVES ARE LOST,
PEOPLE'S THOUGHTS INTERSECT.
NEXT EPISODE:
"WITHIN THE SCATTERING LIGHT".
BEFORE LOVE TURNS
TO HATE.