Revive:
VEDA'S LOCATION?
WELL, I CAN'T SAY
I REALLY KNOW.
YOU'RE AN INNOVATOR AND
YOU DON'T KNOW WHERE IT IS?
OKAY, LET'S SAY I DO KNOW
THE LOCATION.
WHAT DO YOU PEOPLE
INTEND TO DO WITH VEDA?
TAKE IT BACK.
(Chuckles)
BUT ORIGINALLY,
VEDA WAS MADE FOR
WE INNOVATORS TO USE.
OKAY, THEN TELL ME THIS.
IF VEDA SERVES YOU, THEN WHAT
DO YOU INTEND TO USE IT FOR?
WHAT WAS AEOLIA'S REAL GOAL
WHEN HE CREATED HIS PLAN?
IT'S FOR THE DIALOGUES
THAT ARE TO COME.
DIALOGUES THAT ARE TO COME?
(Grunts)
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THAT'S THE LIMITATION OF
BEING HUMAN.
I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE SO PERFECT YOURSELF.
YOU WERE CAPTURED,
AFTER ALL.
DON'T BE ABSURD.
I ALLOWED IT.
YOU WHAT?!
(Gasps)
Feldt:
MISS SUMERAGI!
WHAT'S WRONG, FELDT?
IT'S MISS RETURNER!
WHAT ABOUT ANEW?!
SHE SHOT LASSE AND
TOOK MILEINA HOSTAGE!
Allelujah:
WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
MISS RETURNER SAID SHE WAS
AN INNOVATOR!
AN INNOVATOR?!
SHE SAID THAT?!
BUT HOW?
(Grunts)
DON'T MOVE!
Revive:
YOU KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING,
RIGHT?
IF ANYTHING SHOULD HAPPEN TO ME,
I CANNOT GUARANTEE
THE SAFETY OF THE HOSTAGE.
BECAUSE WE'RE THE SAME TYPE,
ANEW AND I ARE ABLE
TO CONNECT OUR THOUGHTS.
I TRUST YOU UNDERSTAND.
QUANTUM WAVES.
HUH?
(Gasps)
(Thinking)
ANEW, CONTINUE
ACCORDING TO THE PLAN.
(Gasps)
(Startled gasps)
THE SHIPBOARD SYSTEMS!
DAMN IT!
UH, MISS RETURNER,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
EVERYONE WILL FORGIVE YOU‐‐
SHUT UP.
AH! OKAY!
(Gasps)
YOU'RE NOT GETTING OUT OF HERE.
Mileina:
MISS PERIES!
HOW DID YOU FIND ME?
THINK YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO USES QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES?
♪
Sumeragi:
THE SHIPBOARD SYSTEMS HAVE BEEN
INFECTED WITH A VIRUS?!
WE'LL SPLIT INTO TWO GROUPS
AND LOOK FOR MILEINA.
GET TO THE BRIDGE,
MISS SUMERAGI.
ALL RIGHT.
DAMN IT.
WHERE DID ANEW GO?
THIS WAY!
HEY!
YOU CAME TO SAVE ME,
MISS PERIES!
I'M RESCUED!
HMPH.
THE C‐LEVEL
QUANTUM BRAIN WAVE USER.
I FORGOT YOU WERE ON THIS SHIP.
THE DEFECTIVE SUPER SOLDIER.
YOU'RE THE ONES
WHO ARE TO BLAME FOR EVERYTHING!
THIS IS FOR THE COLONEL.
Setsuna:
DON'T DO IT!
Mileina:
MR. SEIEI! MR. STRATOS!
THIS HAS GONE FAR ENOUGH, ANEW!
LYLE.
HMM, WERE YOU PLANNING ON
LEAVING WITHOUT ME?
DID YOU WANT TO COME WITH ME?
YOU'LL WITNESS THE REFORMATION
OF THE WORLD!
HMM, ALL RIGHT!
I LIKE THE SOUND OF THAT!
WHAT?!
AND I'LL BRING
CHERUDIM WITH ME, TOO!
SO THERE YOU HAVE IT,
SETSUNA!
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING
YOU'VE DONE FOR ME.
HMM.
WELL, IF YOU'RE SURE,
SO BE IT!
(Mileina screaming)
LYLE!
(Grunts)
(Mileina yelps)
(Gasps)
(Mileina sobbing)
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO HIT ME!
COME ON!
THEY TOOK BACK THE HOSTAGE?
THAT'S WHAT WE GET
FOR MAKING HER A WOMAN.
THEY GET LOST IN THEIR EMOTIONS.
OH, LYLE.
(Screaming)
Saji:
MR. IAN!
HUH?
ANEW'S GOING TO ESCAPE
IN A SHUTTLE.
WHAT IS WITH THIS SYSTEM?
IT'S COMPLETELY DIFFERENT!
THERE!
Feldt:
THE THIRD HATCH
IS OPENING AUTOMATICALLY!
THE REAR HATCH, TOO!
SEND OUT CHERUDIM AND 00!
ROGER THAT.
Anew:
I'M SORRY. I MESSED THAT UP.
SAVE YOUR EXCUSES FOR RIBBONS.
WILL THE GUNDAMS PURSUE?
Setsuna:
LOCKON.
SORRY, BUT GETTING THE 0 RAISER
BACK TAKES PRECEDENCE.
YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
Lyle:
TRANS AM!
HUH?
THEY'RE USING THEIR TRANS AM!
Setsuna:
GIVE IT UP!
DO YOU REALLY INTEND TO
DAMAGE THIS MACHINE?
NO NEED.
WE HAVE A GREAT TACTICAL
FORECASTER.
WHAT?
Haro:
HA!
(Grunting)
WHAT THE HELL?!
YOU LITTLE!
Haro:
NOW!
0 RAISER! DOCKING MODE!
(Grunts)
00'S CONTROLLING THE SYSTEM!
THE CONTROLS ARE NOT...
Setsuna:
LIKE LOCKON SAID, YOU'RE NOT
SO PERFECT AFTER ALL.
(Grunts)
HMM.
Revive:
THEN I HAVE NO CHOICE.
I'LL GIVE UP THE 0 RAISER.
BUT IT'S GOING TO COST YOU...
TO FIX IT!
(Rapid gunfire)
(Winds down)
Setsuna:
I'VE LOST 0 RAISER'S OUTPUT!
DAMN YOU!
(Gasps)
ANEW!
YOU WOULD SHOOT ME?
(Gasps)
(Grunts)
Lyle:
ANEW, COME BACK!
ANEW RETURNER!
(Grunts)
I'M FIRING.
I'M TARGETED AND FIRING.
WHAT AM I HERE FOR?
WHAT'S MY ROLE?
WHY AM I WITH KATHARON?
WHY AM I WITH CELESTIAL BEING?
(Gasps)
(Screams)
YOU'RE A PATHETIC EXCUSE
FOR A MAN!
LYLE DYLANDY!
IS THAT ALL THE DETERMINATION
YOU COULD MUSTER?!
DAMN IT!
LYLE DYLANDY.
I REALLY DO LOVE YOU.
OH, LYLE.
HMM?
Ribbons:
I HEARD YOU WEREN'T
FEELING WELL.
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
IT WOULD PROBABLY BE
A GOOD IDEA TO PRESCRIBE
SOME NEW MEDICATION FOR YOU.
ALMARK,
I DON'T‐‐
I GAVE YOU THE MEDICATION THAT
SUPPRESSED THE CELLULAR DEFECTS
THAT WERE EATING YOUR BODY.
WHY DID I DO THAT?
(Gasps)
BECAUSE IT'S WHAT YOU WANTED.
SO THAT YOU CAN BRING ABOUT
A UNITED WORLD WITHOUT WAR.
AND AVENGE YOUR PARENTS
BY DEFEATING THE GUNDAMS.
DEFEAT GUNDAMS.
I HAVE SUCH HIGH HOPES FOR YOU.
I BROUGHT THIS REGNANT
SPECIFICALLY FOR YOU.
I WANT YOU TO BECOME
HUMANITY'S FIRST INNOVATOR,
SO YOU CAN GUIDE THIS WORLD.
WILL YOU?
LOUISE HALEVY?
I'LL DO THAT, ALMARK.
HMM.
THAT'S MY GIRL.
Sumeragi:
FELDT, WHAT'S THE CONDITION OF
THE SHIPBOARD SYSTEMS?
Feldt:
NAVIGATION AND COMBAT SYSTEMS
ARE SERIOUSLY DAMAGED.
WE REMOVED THE VIRUS,
BUT 3456 PACKETS OF DATA
WERE COMPLETELY DELETED.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE INNOVATORS
TOOK SOME DATA, TOO.
HOW LONG TILL
EVERYTHING'S RESTORED?
AT LEAST 2210.
MISS SUMERAGI.
WHAT ABOUT MISS RETURNER?
JUST FOCUS ON YOUR WORK FOR NOW.
THE ENEMY'S COMING.
IAN, WHAT'S UP WITH
THE 0 RAISER'S REPAIRS?
WE'VE REPLACED
THE ENTIRE COCKPIT UNIT.
BUT RE‐TUNING THE RAISER
SYSTEM'S GONNA TAKE TIME.
WE WON'T BE ABLE TO LAUNCH 00
FOR A WHILE.
I UNDERSTAND.
HOW COULD THIS HAVE HAPPENED?
ANEW.
HOW COULD YOU?
HOW COULD YOU DO IT?!
DAMN IT!
Setsuna:
WE'RE ABOUT TO SEE HER
ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
(Sighs)
HMM.
I DON'T THINK THEY'RE GONNA
MISS THIS OPPORTUNITY.
YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL ME,
I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
THAT GIRL IS
AN INNOVATOR.
SHE'S OUR ENEMY.
PULLING THE TRIGGER
WILL BE‐‐
DON'T TRY TO ACT TOUGH.
(Grunts)
I'LL BE THE ONE TO
PULL THE TRIGGER.
I DON'T MIND IF YOU HATE ME.
STOP PLAYING
THE HARD CASE, KID!
LOOK, YOU'VE GOT
NO REASON TO FIGHT HER.
SURE, I DO!
YOU'VE MORE OF
A REASON NOT TO FIGHT HER.
HMPH.
TSK.
HUH?
TIERIA. GET SERAVEE
READY FOR LAUNCH.
I'LL HANDLE THINGS HERE.
BUT YOUR SHIP‐HANDLING
SKILLS AREN'T‐‐
I KNOW THEY LEAVE
MUCH TO BE DESIRED.
THAT'S WHY I NEED YOU TO
PROTECT US WITH YOUR GUNDAM.
ROGER.
GETTING READINGS ON
THE E‐SENSOR!
FROM THE SPEED,
THEY'RE PROBABLY ENEMY FORCES!
INNOVATORS.
(Sighs)
ANEW'S COMING.
(Grunts)
Hiling:
THEIR SHIP'S SYSTEMS ARE IN
SHAMBLES, AND 00 IS DAMAGED.
SHOULD BE EASY TAKING OUT
THE REMAINING GUNDAMS.
HILING.
REMEMBER, OUR OBJECTIVE
IS TO CAPTURE THE 00.
BELIEVE ME, I KNOW THAT.
Hiling:
AND THAT'S WHY WE'RE GOING TO
NEED HER HELP
WHEN WE GET THERE.
YOU'RE A TWISTED ONE.
WARRANT OFFICER,
THIS MAY BE THE NEW REGNANT'S
FIRST SORTIE,
BUT WE'RE EXPECTING
A LOT FROM YOU.
ROGER.
Hiling:
THE GUNDAMS ARE HERE!
(Gasps)
THREE MACHINES.
Tieria:
ONLY A FEW ENEMY UNITS, BUT
ONE OF THEM IS A MOBILE ARMOR.
IT'S DIFFERENT
FROM THE PREVIOUS ONE.
Lyle:
INCOMING!
(Grunts)
Tieria:
THAT PARTICLE BEAM!
Lyle:
IT CURVED!
IT'S SO POWERFUL!
Allelujah:
THIS ATTACK...
IT'S GONNA HIT!
NO, IT WON'T!
WHERE?
WHERE ARE YOU, ANEW?!
ENEMY APPROACHING!
HMM?
Anew:
DON'T LOSE YOUR HEAD, LYLE!
YOU'VE GOT AN IMAGE
TO LIVE UP TO!
ANEW, STOP!
THAT'S ANEW?!
Hiling:
(Laughs)
WHAT A DRAMATIC REUNION.
YOUR BELOVED IS AN INNOVATOR
AND YOUR SWORN ENEMY!
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT THEY CALL
A TRULY DANGEROUS LIAISON!
THIS WON'T END WELL.
Allelujah:
LOCKON!
(Grunts)
ANEW'S TAKEN ONE MACHINE
WITH HER!
WE'LL DEAL WITH THE REST!
Allelujah:
(Grunts)
IF THIS BEAM HITS...
Tieria:
I'LL MAKE AN OPENING!
HYPER BURST MODE!
HIGH DENSITY
COMPRESSED PARTICLES,
RELEASING!
IMPOSSIBLE!
THE HYPER BURST WAS...
(Grunts)
Allelujah:
TIERIA!
(Grunts)
(Screams)
Peries:
HOW DARE YOU!
Feldt:
ARIOS IS DAMAGED!
CHERUDIM IS STILL HEADING AWAY
FROM THE COMBAT AIRSPACE!
ISN'T 00 READY, YET?!
Ian:
A LITTLE MORE TIME!
Sumeragi:
HURRY!
WAIT, LYLE.
Anew:
FANGS, FLY!
HARO, DEPLOY THE SHIELD BITS
IN ASSAULT MODE!
Lyle:
WHY?!
WHY DO WE HAVE TO FIGHT
EACH OTHER LIKE THIS?!
Anew:
IT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE A HUMAN.
AND OBVIOUSLY,
I AM AN INNOVATOR!
(Grunts)
WE UNDERSTOOD EACH OTHER!
IT WAS A FALSE REALITY!
YOU'RE SAYING IT WAS ALL A LIE?
THE THINGS I WANTED,
AND THE THINGS YOU FELT?!
(Grunts)
HAVE IT YOUR WAY!
OH, LYLE.
(Grunts)
IT'S ABOUT TIME WE GOT GOING!
THEY BROKE THROUGH!
Tieria, Allelujah, Peries:
(Screaming)
UH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Lyle:
IT'S OBVIOUS, ISN'T IT?
I'M GONNA DO MY BEST
TO MAKE YOU MY WOMAN AGAIN!
AND I'M NOT TAKING NO
FOR AN ANSWER!
BUT...
BUT, LYLE...
I'M GETTING WHAT I WANT.
EVEN IF YOU ARE
NOTHING BUT AN INNOVATOR.
(Gasps)
OH, LYLE.
YOU'RE MINE NOW!
00!
(Growls)
Lyle:
ANEW.
COME BACK, ANEW.
OH, LYLE.
I FEEL...
I FEEL LIKE I...
(Gasps)
FOOLISH HUMAN.
ANEW?
(Yelps)
(Screams)
Lyle:
ANEW!
INNOVATORS ARE MEANT TO
GUIDE HUMANITY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE ARE SUPERIOR BEINGS,
ABSOLUTE AND PERFECT.
I CAN'T STAND US BEING TREATED
AS THOUGH WE WERE
AS LOWLY AS HUMANS.
Ribbon and Anew: LET ME SHOW YOU
THE REAL DIFFERENCE IN OUR
POWERS.
Lyle:
STOP IT!
ANEW!
STOP DOING THIS!
(Grunts)
Anew:
(Attack yell)
ANEW!
(Glass shatters)
THAT...
THAT WAS...
Anew:
LYLE,
YOU KNOW, I'M GLAD
I WAS AN INNOVATOR.
HMM?
WHY IS THAT?
IF I WASN'T ONE, THEN I WOULD
NEVER HAVE MET YOU.
WE WOULD'VE NEVER HAD
A CHANCE
TO KNOW EACH OTHER
IN THIS WORLD.
HMM.
THAT WOULD'VE BEEN ALL RIGHT.
IF IT MEANT THAT
YOU COULD GO ON LIVING.
YES, BUT WITHOUT YOU
LIFE WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
WORTH LIVING.
ANEW.
LYLE.
WE UNDERSTOOD EACH OTHER,
DIDN'T WE?
HMM?
YEAH, OF COURSE WE DID.
THAT'S GOOD.
♪
Lyle:
(Screaming)
YOU BASTARD! YOU BASTARD!
YOU KILLED ANEW!
Tieria:
LYLE, STOP IT!
SHUT UP!
SHE WAS TRYING TO COME BACK.
SHE WAS GONNA COME BACK TO US,
NOT AS AN INNOVATOR,
BUT AS A HUMAN!
BUT BECAUSE OF YOU SHE'S DEAD!
(Gasps)
BECAUSE OF YOU...
(Sobbing)
ANEW.
(Lyle screaming)
(Thinking)
EVEN THOUGH
THEY UNDERSTOOD EACH OTHER.
EVEN SO...
ONE DAY, LOUISE AND I...
♪ WHERE ARE YOU NOW? ♪
♪ HOW ARE YOU FRIEND? ♪
A VOICE IS ECHOING.
HER VOICE.
HER SONG.
Narrator:
THOSE WHOSE LIVES
HAVE BEEN CHANGED.
THOSE WHO HAVE LOST FAMILY.
IS THE CHAIN OF HATRED
SATISFIED ONLY BY TAKING LIVES?
NEXT EPISODE:
"THE DOOR OF CHANGE".
SETSUNA HEADS THROUGH
TO THE OTHER SIDE.