Operator:
WE HAVE VISUAL
ON THE SATELLITE WEAPON.
WE'LL BE WITHIN STRIKING
RANGE SHORTLY, SIR.
WHAT'S THE CURRENT STATUS
OF THE SECOND FLEET?
IT'S APPROACHING
ITS DESIGNATED POINT NOW, SIR
VERY GOOD.
AS SOON AS IT REACHES POSITION,
THE TWO FLEETS WILL
BEGIN CONDUCTING
STAGGERED MISSILE
ATTACKS ON THE TARGET.
CAPTAIN.
THE SATELLITE WEAPON
IS MOVING!
IT'S MOVING?!
Operator:
TH‐THE LASER BARREL IS
EMERGING FROM THE TOP!
THAT ANGLE HAS IT POINTED
AT THE SECOND FLEET!
(Blast)
HALF OF THE SECOND FLEET WAS
JUST WIPED OUT, SIR!
(Frustrated grunt)
CAPTAIN!
FIRE MISSILES?!
NOT YET! I DON'T THINK
THEY CAN FIRE ANOTHER BLAST
FROM THAT THING
SO SOON.
WE NEED TO GET CLOSER
JUST TO MAKE SURE
WE'LL BE ABLE HIT IT!
PARTICLE BEAM!
WHAT?!
(Blast)
TOO FAR FOR YOU TO FIRE,
BUT I'VE GOT MUCH GREATER RANGE!
♪
(High pitch charge)
(Blast)
(Boom)
SHIPS SEVEN AND NINE WERE
DESTROYED, SIR!
LAUNCH MOBILE SUIT TEAMS.
HAVE THEM PROTECT
THE MISSILE CARRIERS.
WE CAN'T AFFORD TO TAKE
ANY MORE LOSSES.
HUH?
WE JUST LOST SHIP TWO!
(Groans)
CAPTAIN!
BEGIN THE MISSILE ATTACK
AT ONCE!
HAVE ALL SHIPS
LAUNCH A MISSILE BARRAGE!
NINETY‐THREE PERCENT
OF THE MISSILES
WERE SHOT DOWN BY
THEIR DEFENSES, SIR!
BUT‐BUT WE FIRED
SO MANY!
WE HAVE INCOMING
ENEMY MOBILE SUITS, SIR!
MOBILE SUIT TEAMS
TO INTERCEPT.
(Lasers blasting)
(Boom)
(Screaming)
HOW RUDE.
DON'T JUST RUN IN THERE
AND STEAL MY PREY.
Operator:
IT'S HOPELESS,
WE'RE COMPLETELY OUTMATCHED!
NO MATTER WHAT, WE HAVE TO
BREAK THROUGH THE ENEMY!
THE SECOND FLEET
ONLY HAS THREE SHIPS LEFT!
ONLY ONE OF THEM HAS TO MAKE IT!
APPROACH THE SATELLITE WEAPON
AND RAM INTO IT!
CAPTAIN!
(Loud blast)
(Boom)
RE‐REINFORCEMENTS?
HUH? THAT MACHINE, IT'S...
HERE IT COMES.
Setsuna:
ATTENTION KATHARON FLEET,
THIS IS CELESTIAL BEING.
WE'LL CARRY OUT THE MISSION TO
DESTROY THE SATELLITE WEAPON.
WE'RE GRATEFUL FOR
YOUR ASSISTANCE.
WE'D LIKE WHATEVER DATA
YOU HAVE ON YOUR TARGET.
SEND IT OVER CHANNEL 34.
OKAY, WE'RE SENDING IT
OVER RIGHT AWAY.
(Monitor beeps)
TRANSMISSION DONE.
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
THE WEAPON WILL FIRE AGAIN.
MOVE YOUR FORCES BELOW
THE ORBITAL RING.
WE'RE MOVING NOW.
THIS IS IT. THE A‐LAWS'
SATELLITE WEAPON.
A GUNDAM
HAS APPEARED, SIR!
LOOKS LIKE FOUR MOBILE SUITS
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED, SIR.
SO YOU DECIDED TO SHOW UP
AFTER ALL, CELESTIAL BEING.
IS THE MEMENTO MORI
RECHARGED YET?
THE RESONANCE RATE IS AT
TWENTY‐SEVEN PERCENT, SIR.
CAPTAIN HILING CARE WILL
DEAL WITH THE GUNDAM.
OUR FORCES WILL TAKE
A DEFENSIVE STANCE.
PREPARE FOR AN ASSAULT BY
THE ENEMY SHIPS.
YES, SIR.
THEIR OBJECTIVE WILL BE
TO DESTROY THE MEMENTO MORI.
IN THAT CASE,
WE'LL SIMPLY STRIKE THEM DOWN
AS THEY DRAW NEAR.
I'LL SHOW YOU WHY
I LOVE MOPPING UP
OPERATIONS SO MUCH.
(Lasers blasting)
(Boom)
RIBBONS IS INTERESTED
IN THIS BOY.
THAT MAKES ME JEALOUS.
THAT PARTICLE OUTPUT.
IT'S A NEW MODEL!
YOU HAVE SOME SKILLS, BOY.
(Gasps)
(Frustrated grunt)
EVEN IF THE PARTICLES WERE
A LITTLE MORE DIFFUSED.
TO HAVE THE SAME RANGE
AS THE GADESSA IS...
(Grunts)
Operator:
CAPTAIN CARE,
DON'T LEAVE YOUR POSITION!
MAJOR, IT'S THE GADESSA!
THE CAPTAIN HAS A LICENSE.
LET HER DO WHAT SHE WANTS.
HMM.
WELCOME BACK FROM YOUR VISIT,
MY MISTRESS.
HUH? DID SOMETHING
HAPPEN TO YOU?
HOWEVER SUPERIOR HE IS...
A MAN'S JEALOUSY
IS AN UGLY THING TO SEE.
NOW THEN,
HOW'S THE BATTLE COMING?
THE PTOLEMAOIS, HAS NOT
YET LAUNCHED
A DIRECT ATTACK
ON THE SATELLITE WEAPON.
Liu Mei:
I SEE. THEY'RE BEING CAUTIOUS.
(Giggles)
OH, MY MISTRESS.
I'D SAY A WOMAN'S JEALOUSY
IS JUST AS UGLY.
I'M GOING TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU DON'T GET YOUR WAY.
HARO.
GOTCHA! GOTCHA!
I'M DISPLAYING THE DATA
THE DOUBLE 0 RAISER
SENT US ABOUT
THE SATELLITE WEAPON.
LIKE WE THOUGHT,
A FREE‐ELECTRON LASER STRAFING
DEVICE THAT HAS ACCESS
TO THE ORBITAL RING'S
PARTICLE ACCELERATOR.
Feldt:
AND THE WAY THOSE
ESCORT SHIPS ARE DEPLOYED.
AS YOU FORECAST, MISS SUMERAGI.
THE LASER BARREL ONLY HAS
A LIMITED FIRING ANGLE.
HUH?
MISS NORIEGA, WE'RE RECEIVING
WHAT LOOKS LIKE
SOME CODED DATA FROM AN AGENT!
FROM WANG LIU MEI?
WHERE WAS SHE ALL THIS TIME?
PUT IT ON SCREEN,
MILEINA.
YOU GOT IT!
IT'S STRUCTURAL DATA ON
THE SATELLITE WEAPON.
HOW DID SHE MANAGE
TO GET THESE?
Feldt:
MISS SUMERAGI!
THERE'S THE WEAPON'S
WEAK POINT.
THE ELECTROMAGNETIC RESONATOR!
THEN I GUESS THAT DETERMINES
OUR MISSION PLAN.
WE'LL APPROACH THE WEAPON
THROUGH ITS BLIND SPOT
AND THEN LAUNCH
A DIRECT ASSAULT.
TIERIA AND LOCKON WILL
HAVE TO COORDINATE
WITH THE UTMOST PRECISION.
AND ITS DEFENSIVE FORCES?
WE'LL CHARGE RIGHT
PAST THEM.
IS THIS PLAN ABOUT PRECISION
OR BRUTE FORCE?
WE'RE GOING TO NEED BOTH.
ALL RIGHT, TIME TO GET THIS
MISSION UNDERWAY.
Everyone:
ROGER!
I SENT IT! I SENT IT!
THANK YOU, HARO!
NOW, WE JUST GOT TO
GO GET THEM!
(Giggles)
YOU KNOW LOUISE?
YES. ALTHOUGH,
RIGHT AFTER SHE WAS
GIVEN HER OFFICIAL DUTY
ASSIGNMENT, I CAME HERE.
SO, LOUISE
IS A MOBILE SUIT?
YES, SHE WAS A PILOT.
I KNEW IT.
I KNEW WHEN IT WAS HAPPENING
THAT LOUISE HAD TO BE
SOMEWHERE CLOSE BY.
(Phone ringing)
Sumeragi:
COME TO THE BRIDGE, PLEASE.
AND BRING SAJI WITH YOU.
WE'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
AND ALSO...
I THINK I'M GOING TO NEED YOUR
HELP WITH SOMETHING.
(Crash)
AND THAT MAKES EIGHT.
SETSUNA, BE AWARE WE'RE STARTING
THE MISSION NOW.
ROGER.
ALL GUNDAMS ARE IN THEIR
ASSIGNED POSITIONS.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
LET'S DO THIS.
NOW YOU'RE MINE!
COMMENCING MISSION!
(Grunts)
(Blast)
Setsuna:
THE NEW MODEL TOOK THE BAIT!
(Yelling)
(Clash)
INNOVATOR!
SO YOU KNOW WHAT I AM!
WHAT THE‐‐
HERE IT COMES!
ALL GUNPORTS OPEN AND READY!
543 SECONDS UNTIL PTOLEMY
REACHES THE TARGET!
I'M COUNTING ON YOU TWO.
TIERIA, LOCKON.
ENEMY SHIP SIGHTED!
THEY'RE APPROACHING US ALONG THE
LENGTH OF THE ORBITAL RING, SIR!
AS EXPECTED, THEY'RE RIGHT IN
MEMENTO MORI'S BLIND SPOT.
INTERCEPTION FLEET,
BEGIN FIRING!
FORCE THEM UP INTO
THE WEAPON'S LINE OF FIRE!
(Lasers blasting)
Sumeragi:
LASSE!
HANG ON!
(Lasers continue firing)
WATCH IT, THE SHIP IS BEING
FORCED OFF
THE PATH TO THE RIGHT!
(Beeping)
ENTERING SATELLITE WEAPON'S LINE
OF FIRE IN FOURTEEN SECONDS!
RIGHT...
MEMENTO MORI IS
FULLY CHARGED, SIR!
GET READY TO FIRE.
YES, SIR!
BEGINNING RESONANCE!
(Chuckles)
(Beeping)
PTOLEMY HAS ENTERED THE ENEMY
SATELLITE WEAPON'S LINE OF FIRE!
(Everyone screams)
(Worried sigh)
(Warning alert buzzes)
(Feldt screams)
MISS SUMERAGI!
NOT YET, NOT YET!
YEAH, BUT‐‐
I SAID, NOT YET!
MEMENTO MORI,
COMMENCE STRAFING!
RIGHT NOW!
ALLELLUJAH!
(Blasts and rumbles)
(Appreciative sigh)
(Hiling laughing)
IT'S ALL OVER NOW.
(Groans)
STRAFING COMPLETE, SIR.
(Scoffs)
NOW FOR CAPTAIN CARE TO FINISH
OFF THE DOUBLE POWERED ONE.
MAJOR! THE ENEMY SHIP!
IT'S GONE!
HUH?
THAT‐THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
TRANS AM ON.
ATTACK THE ENEMY SHIP!
BEGIN RECHARGING
THE MEMENTO MORI!
R‐ROGER THAT, SIR!
DECK THREE,
HATCH IS FULLY OPEN!
Feldt:
SERAVEE AND CHERUDIM
ARE IN ATTACK POSITION!
(Bracing grunts)
RIGHT NOW ALL OF ARIOS'
TRANS AM POWER
IS BEING DEVOTED
TO PTOLEMY'S THRUSTERS.
SO WE CAN'T USE OUR GN FIELD.
Sumeragi:
LOCKON!
Lyle:
ALL RIGHT! TRANS AM!
LET'S GET GOING, HARO!
DEPLOY SHIELD BITS!
(Blasts)
(Lasers ricochet)
ARIOS' TRANS AM HAS
NINETY‐FOUR SECONDS LEFT
UNTIL IT REACHES ITS
TIME LIMIT!
NOT THERE YET.
THE BITS AREN'T GOING TO
HOLD UP AT THIS RATE!
Sumeragi:
HOLD ON JUST A LITTLE LONGER!
(Boom)
HOW DARE YOU,
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT VERMIN!
(Hiling yelps)
I AM YOUR OPPONENT!
PREPARE YOURSELF!
Operator:
THEY'VE BROKEN THROUGH
THE INTERCEPTION FLEET!
CONCENTRATE ALL OUR FIRE!
CHARGING?
TWENTY‐EIGHT PERCENT, SIR!
(Frustrated grunt)
(Smash)
SHIELD IS ALMOST USED UP!
NO, NOT YET!
A LITTLE LONGER!
(Worried screams)
CLOSER, GET A LITTLE CLOSER.
(Whimper)
ARIOS HAS REACHED
ITS TRANS AM TIME LIMIT!
I'M GOING TO MAKE THIS
PLAN SUCCEED.
CHERUDIM'S SHIELD BITS
ARE NOW GONE!
WHATEVER IT TAKES!
(Groaning)
I'LL PROTECT EVERYONE!
WITH MY TACTICS!
TIERIA!
ROGER! TRANS AM!
HYPER BURST, NOW TRIGGERING
MAXIMUM RELEASE!
(Whimpering)
(Boom)
THIS IS IT, LAUNCH ALL
GN MISSILES!
HERE THEY COME!
(Multiple explosions)
(Startled breath)
(Sighs)
(Rindt laughs)
LOOKS LIKE YOU DIDN'T HAVE
QUITE ENOUGH FIREPOWER.
IT WASN'T STRONG ENOUGH
TO DESTROY
THE MEMENTO MORI'S
ELECTROMAGNETIC RESONATOR.
MAJOR!
HMM?
WHAT‐WHAT THE‐‐
(Gasps)
Rindt:
IS THAT A...
(Focused sigh)
Lyle:
THE ELECTROMAGNETIC
OPTICAL RESONATOR.
I HAVE JUST ONE CHANCE.
LOCKON.
LYLE.
(Tensed moan)
LOCKON!
YOU ARE LOCKON STRATOS!
JUST LIKE
THE NAME SAYS...
TARGETED AND FIRING!
(Blasts)
(Boom)
(Burst)
(Whimpering)
NO!
(Boom)
Feldt:
CONFIRMING, THE SATELLITE
WEAPON HAS BEEN DESTROYED!
PTOLEMY IS TO MAINTAIN
ITS PRESENT SPEED
AND WITHDRAW FROM THIS SECTOR.
YOU CAN CALL BACK
THE DOUBLE 0 RAISER.
ROGER THAT!
WITHDRAWAL ACKNOWLEDGED.
Hiling:
HOW DARE YOU! HUH?
WHAT? BACKUP?!
(Gasps)
(Crack)
DAMN YOU, GUNDAM!
(Growls)
MY BACKUP... HAD A RED BEAM.
IT'S A MACHINE WITH
A PSEUDO SOLAR REACTOR.
(Giggles)
♪
LOOK, KLAUS.
THEY ACTUALLY DID IT.
THEY MIGHT'VE JUST SAVED
THE MIDDLE EAST.
OH WOW!
IT'S PRETTY.
NO, CHILDREN.
THERE'S NOTHING PRETTY
ABOUT THOSE LIGHTS
IN THE SKY.
THOSE ARE THE LIGHTS OF
A FAR OFF BATTLE,
A TERRIBLE THING
WE DON'T WANT TO PASS ON
TO YOUR GENERATION.
WHAT SHOULD WE PASS ON
TO THIS GENERATION?
SO, THE SATELLITE HAS FALLEN.
(Door opens)
MOST LIKELY, IT WAS
THE WORK OF CELESTIAL BEING.
HERCURY!
COLONEL PANG HERCURY!
IT SURE HAS BEEN A WHILE.
HELLO, WILD BEAR OF RUSSIA!
Narrator:
SEPARATED FROM THE PTOLEMAIOS,
SETSUNA RETURNS
TO A PLACE FROM THE PAST
TO FINALLY MEET THE EXECUTOR
OF THE MASTER PLAN.
NEXT EPISODE:
"I CAN HEAR A SONG".
WHEN SHE SINGS,
IT PIERCES THE HEART.