Interrogator:
DURING THE AZADISTAN CIVIL WAR
FOUR YEARS AGO,
YOU WERE IN CONTACT WITH
A MEMBER OF
CELESTIAL BEING, WEREN'T YOU?
Marina:
I ALREADY TOLD YOU
ALL ABOUT IT
FOUR YEARS AGO.
WELL, THE SITUATION
HAS CHANGED SINCE THEN.
NOW THAT NEW GUNDAMS HAVE
APPEARED ON THE SCENE,
YOU HAVE ONCE AGAIN BECOME
A PERSON OF
TREMENDOUS IMPORTANCE TO US.
(Sighs)
MARINA ISMAIL,
PRINCESS ROYAL OF
THE KINGDOM OF AZADISTAN.
♪
Secretary General:
THE ASSEMBLY HAS DECIDED
TO PLACE THE FEDERAL
SECURITY AGENCY
UNDER THE DIRECT CONTROL
OF THE AUTONOMOUS
PEACEKEEPING FORCE.
WE NOW HAVE
SOME 40 MILLION SOLDIERS.
THE ESTABLISHMENT
OF THIS FORCE
COULD NOT HAVE OCCURRED
WITHOUT VEDA'S INFORMATION
CONTROL CAPABILITIES.
Ribbons:
IT WAS AN HONOR
TO ASSIST YOU.
THE FEDERATION GOVERNMENT
SHOULDN'T HAVE TO GIVE IN
TO PETTY RESISTANCE.
FOR ANY DIALOGUES
IN THE FUTURE.
Secretary General:
WE HAVE GREAT HOPES FOR
WHAT YOU ARE DOING.
OF COURSE YOU DO.
IT'S THE REASON WE WERE BORN.
IT'S WHY WE EXIST.
I AM FAITHFULLY EXECUTING
AEOLIA SCHENBERG'S PLAN.
SOMETHING NO HUMAN CAN DO.
AND ONLY WE CAN,
FOR WE ARE THE INNOVATORS.
Regene:
REGARDING
THE AZADISTAN PRINCESS,
YOU'VE BEEN LEAVING HER
ALONE UNTIL NOW.
SO WHAT MADE YOU CHANGE
YOUR MIND?
(Chuckles)
YOU KNOW THE REASON.
HMPH.
SO, YOU REALLY THINK
THEY'LL SHOW UP?
OF COURSE THEY WILL.
AFTER ALL,
ONE OF THE GUNDAM MEISTERS
IS BEING HELD THERE TOO.
WAKE UP,
TEST SUBJECT E‐57.
(Groggy moaning)
SO THIS IS THE MAN.
THE GUNDAM PILOT
YOU'VE BEEN HOLDING HERE
FOR THE LAST FOUR YEARS.
(Gasps)
(Muffled shouting)
HMM?
Peries: (Thinking)
MY QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES
AREN'T AFFECTING HIM ANYMORE.
THE FILE REPORT SAYS
IT'S BECAUSE OF A HEAD INJURY
HE SUFFERED.
Allelujah:
(Panting)
MARIE.
(Sighs)
YOU FINALLY CAME.
IT IS YOU,
YOU SURVIVED SOMEHOW.
MARIE.
MARIE?
(Gasps)
BUT IT'S ME!
YOU AND I USED TO TALK
ALL THE TIME IN THE HOME!
IT'S ALLELUJAH!
STOP TALKING LIKE THAT,
MY NAME IS NOT MARIE!
NO.
YOU'RE MARIE,
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
Tieria:
DO YOU HAVE ANY MOBILE SUIT
COMBAT EXPERIENCE?
OBVIOUSLY, I DON'T.
BUT I HAVE OPERATED
AN INDUSTRIAL WORK LOADER.
SO HE BROUGHT US SOMEONE
WHO'S A COMPLETE NOVICE.
DAMN SETSUNA.
THAT JUST MEANS
I'VE GOT A LOT OF THINGS
I NEED TO LEARN.
SO I'M COUNTING ON YOU,
MY OH‐SO‐CHARMING
INSTRUCTOR.
I'D PREFER LESS TEASING!
LYLE DYLANDY.
MILEINA, HAVE ARIOS AND
CHERUDIM BEEN LOADED YET?
Mileina:
ALL FINISHED!
AND WHAT'S MISS SUMERAGI
DOING NOW?
SHE'S STILL SHUTTING
HERSELF UP IN HER ROOM.
Lasse and Mileina:
(Worried sigh)
Ian:
SHE SAYS SHE ISN'T
NECESSARILY GOING TO
REJOIN CELESTIAL BEING.
Setsuna:
YES, THE RECORDS HAVE IT RIGHT.
OUR GROUP HAD A DIFFERENT
POINT OF VIEW FROM THE THRONES
WHEN IT CAME TO
ARMED INTERVENTIONS.
SO THEY WEREN'T YOUR ALLIES?
NO.
(Gasps)
HMM.
EVEN SO, YOU KILLED PEOPLE
WITH YOUR GUNDAMS, TOO.
HURTING THEIR LOVED ONES
LIKE I'VE BEEN HURT.
IT'S ONLY NATURAL FOR PEOPLE
TO HATE YOU
FOR WHAT YOU DID.
I KNOW THAT.
THE WORLD WAS PEACEFUL
BACK THEN.
MY NORMAL EVERYDAY LIFE
WOULD HAVE CONTINUED,
AND IT WAS YOU PEOPLE
WHO DESTROYED ALL THAT!
SO EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT
AS LONG AS
YOU HAVE PEACE?
(Bothered gasp)
I DON'T MEAN THAT.
BUT, NO ONE WANTS
TO BE UNHAPPY.
Sergei:
LIEUTENANT,
NOTICE ANYTHING UNUSUAL
AFTER YOUR TRANSFER
TO THE A‐LAWS?
NO, NOT REALLY.
JUST THE FACT THERE'S MORE
TRAINING THAN USUAL, I GUESS.
I SEE.
UH, COLONEL,
IN THE FILES
ON THE SUPER HUMAN INSTITUTE,
WAS THERE ANYTHING ABOUT
A PERSON NAMED MARIE?
MARIE?
NO, I DON'T RECALL THE NAME.
AND I'M PRETTY SURE
I WENT THROUGH ALL THE FILES
WE COLLECTED FROM THAT PLACE.
IS THAT SO?
(Knock on door)
HMM?
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I'M STILL ON DUTY.
OF COURSE.
COME IN.
LIEUTENANT, THE MAIN FORCE
IS ARRIVING NOW.
VERY GOOD.
ONCE THEY MAKE CONTACT,
HAVE EVERYONE TAKE
THEIR STATIONS.
YES, MA'AM.
Kati:
ASSUME DEFENSIVE POSITIONS
IN ACCORDANCE
WITH THE MISSION PLAN.
CONTACT LIEUTENANT PERIES
OF THE ADVANCE TEAM.
YES, MA'AM.
SO, THIS IS WHERE
THEY'RE HOLDING
THE PILOT OF
THE WINGED ONE.
EVER SINCE WE HANDED HIM OVER
TO THE TOP BRASS,
THERE HASN'T BEEN ANY WORD
ABOUT WHAT'S BECOME OF HIM.
BUT THE A‐LAWS KNEW
WHERE HE WAS.
Nena:
I'VE CONFIRMED
THE INFORMATION FROM LEVEL TWO
ABOUT THE MEISTER STILL
BEING ALIVE.
AND THE A‐LAWS HAVE
JUST SHOWN UP.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO,
MISTRESS?
ANY SUGGESTIONS?
I'LL HANDLE IT FROM HERE.
YOU MAY RETURN NOW.
ROGER THAT!
Allelujah:
MARIE.
WHY DID YOU CHANGE YOUR NAME?
AND YOU TALK LIKE
A STRANGER.
THEY MUST HAVE GIVEN HER
A DIFFERENT PERSONALITY.
Feldt:
WE HAVE A CODED MESSAGE
FROM WANG LIU MEI.
A DISSIDENT DETENTION CENTER
IN THE HRL‐‐
(Surprised gasp)
IS HOLDING ALLELUJAH HAPTISM!
I KNOW HIM!
HE'S ONE OF
THE GUNDAM MEISTERS!
I SEE.
HE WAS CAPTURED BY
THE FEDERATION!
NO WONDER WE COULDN'T
FIGURE OUT WHERE HE WAS.
FELDT,
GET EVERYONE TOGETHER.
WE'RE HAVING A BRIEFING.
WHAT?!
THEY FOUND OUT
WHERE ALLELUJAH IS?!
ALLELUJAH?
WHO ARE THEY TALKING ABOUT?
YOUR BUDDY! YOUR BUDDY!
SO THEY FOUND HIM.
(Grunts)
(Gasps)
COLONEL!
WHY HAVE WE SUSPENDED
OUR SEARCH FOR THE GUNDAMS, SIR?
BECAUSE IT'S
NO LONGER NECESSARY.
NOT NECESSARY?!
IT APPEARS HEADQUARTERS
HAS DANGLED SOME BAIT
FOR CELESTIAL BEING.
I FEEL SORRY
FOR THE GROUND FORCES,
BUT THIS COULD BE
A GOOD CHANCE
TO MEASURE
THE ENEMY'S STRENGTH.
IS IT TRUE,
YOU KNOW WHERE
THEY'RE HOLDING ALLELUJAH?
YEAH, THIS IS
RELIABLE INFORMATION
FROM WANG LIU MEI.
WE'RE GETTING STARTED ON
A RESCUE MISSION NOW.
SO HOW ARE YOU GOING TO
RESCUE HIM?
THAT'S WHAT
WE WANT YOU TO FIGURE OUT.
(Shocked gasp)
MISS SUMERAGI,
WE'D LIKE ONE OF YOUR
TACTICAL FORECASTS.
BUT I'M...
IF HE'S WITH US,
THEN WE CAN START
MOUNTING OPERATIONS
WITH FOUR GUNDAMS AGAIN.
HEY, I'M STILL
NOT TOO SURE ABOUT THIS.
HMPH!
OOPSY.
PLEASE, HELP US OUT.
WE CAN SAVE ALLELUJAH!
(Sighs)
MISS SUMERAGI.
TAKE THIS.
(Gasps)
STOP IT!
I CAN'T LIVE UP TO
YOUR EXPECTATIONS ANYMORE!
MY FORECASTS CAN'T REALLY
CHANGE ANYTHING
THAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
I'D JUST BE PUTTING
EVERYONE IN DANGER!
THERE ARE NO REGRETS!
(Gasps)
EVEN IF THE MISSION FAILS,
WE'LL NEVER
BLAME YOU FOR IT.
Setsuna:
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
ALLELUJAH IS OUR COMRADE.
AND WE'RE GOING TO
SAVE HIM!
SO PLEASE, WORK OUT
A TACTICAL PLAN FOR US.
FELDT,
LATER, COULD YOU
UPDATE ME ON
OUR CURRENT
FIGHTING STRENGTH
AND OUR PRESENT SITUATION,
PLEASE?
YES, MISS SUMERAGI!
Feldt:
WE JUST RECEIVED THIS DATA
FROM WANG LIU MEI.
INCREDIBLE!
THE NAME OF EVERY DETAINEE
AND THEIR LOCATION.
(Startled gasp)
IT'S HER.
IF WE CAN KEEP THIS CARRIER
FROM USING
ITS PARTICLE BEAMS...
AND THEN THERE'S THIS.
LYLE DYLANDY'S ABILITY SCORES
ARE VERY HIGH.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Feldt:
00, SERAVEE, CHERUDIM,
PREPARE TO LAUNCH.
WE'LL FINALLY
SEE SOME ACTION!
I DON'T IMAGINE YOU'LL BE
SEEING MUCH OF IT TODAY.
WELL, THAT MAKES ME FEEL
A LOT BETTER!
(Announcement on PA)
SO, WHAT'S ALL
THIS EXCITEMENT ABOUT?
WHAT ARE THEY GETTING READY FOR
OUT THERE?
RESCUING A BUDDY!
A BUDDY?
COMMENCING MISSION!
THEY'RE GONNA FIGHT AGAIN.
Mileina:
EQUIPPING SERAVEE
WITH BAZOOKAS!
THE TWIN DRIVE IS WORKING,
BUT IT'S STILL A LONG WAY
FROM BEING STABLE.
AND DON'T YOU DARE
USE THE TRANS‐AM!
Setsuna:
ROGER.
MISS SUMERAGI HAS JUST
SUBMITTED A MISSION PLAN!
HEY, WHAT KIND OF PLAN
IS THIS ANYWAY?
NOW, THAT'S DARING!
A BLITZKRIEG ATTACK IN
JUST 300 SECONDS.
HMM.
THAT'S THE SUMERAGI LEE NORIEGA
I KNOW.
Lyle:
OH? I HAVE A JOB, TOO!
BUT, FRANKLY,
THIS'LL WORK BETTER FOR ME.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
JUST TALKING TO MYSELF.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU
FOR SUPPORT,
MR. HARO, SIR!
Mileina:
PTOLEMAIOS, COMMENCING
ATMOSPHERIC ENTRY SEQUENCE.
Feldt:
00, SERAVEE, CHERUDIM,
PREPARE TO LAUNCH.
MISSION WILL COMMENCE AT 0043.
ARIOS WILL STAND BY
IN LAUNCHING POSITION.
SETSUNA.
WHAT IS IT?
ACCORDING TO
WANG LIU MEI'S DATA,
IN THE SAME CENTER
WHERE ALLELUJAH IS BEING HELD,
WE SPOTTED THIS NAME.
(Startled gasp)
Setsuna:
MARINA?
MARINA ISMAIL.
SHE'S IN THE SAME PRISON
AS ALLELUJAH.
Feldt:
GN FIELD AT MAXIMUM OUTPUT.
COMMENCING ATMOSPHERIC ENTRY.
Operator:
COLONEL. MESSAGE
FROM A PILLAR OBSERVATORY.
IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY'VE DETECTED SOMETHING
ENTERING THE ATMOSPHERE.
IT APPEARS TO BE
A CARRIER CLASS SHIP.
IMPOSSIBLE!
IF THEIR SPACESHIP ITSELF
CAN DESCEND TO THE SURFACE...
PREPARE FOR ATTACK!
ALL MOBILE SUIT TEAMS
DEPLOY IMMEDIATELY!
LIEUTENANT PERIES,
WE'RE UNDER ATTACK.
Kati:
SEE TO E‐57.
ROGER THAT.
Andrei:
ALREADY?!
GUNDAMS.
OUR MOBILE SUIT HANGAR!
HURRY!
IT'S CELESTIAL BEING'S
SPACESHIP, MA'AM!
ALL CANNONS, FIRE!
THEY'RE NOT SLOWING DOWN!
THEY WOULDN'T DARE.
GN FIELD, MAXIMUM OUTPUT!
PTOLEMY, DIVING MODE!
STRAIGHT INTO THE WATER!
(Grunting)
(Frightened cries)
Operator:
THE ENEMY SHIP IS
TRAVELING UNDERWATER, MA'AM!
FIRE MISSILES IN RESPONSE!
YES, MA'AM!
Kati:
THIS MUST BE A TACTIC
THEY CAME UP WITH
TO HALVE THE STRENGTH
OF OUR PARTICLE BEAMS.
SETSUNA, TIERIA.
THEIR PARTICLE BEAMS WILL BE
DIFFUSED FOR 300 SECONDS.
THAT'S ALL THE TIME
YOU'VE GOT.
ROGER.
IT'LL TAKE THREE MINUTES.
WHY DON'T WE SAVE
ONE MORE PERSON
WITH THE REMAINING
TWO MINUTES?
MARINA.
(Grunts)
(Screams)
(Screaming)
(Nervous gasp)
WH‐WHAT NOW?
WHAT DOES THIS SHAKING MEAN?
Mileina:
ENEMY MOBILE SUITS
ARE LAUNCHING!
Lasse:
CHERUDIM,
BEGIN RIFLE BOMBARDMENT!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HIT ANYTHING,
JUST KEEP THEM DUCKING!
ROGER!
HUH.
HEY, HARO?
IS THERE SOMETHING COOL
MY BROTHER WOULD SAY
WHEN HE WAS FIGHTING?
TARGETED AND FIRING!
(Chuckles)
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
CHERUDIM GUNDAM,
LOCKON STRATOS,
TARGETED AND FIRING!
LOOK AT THAT PARTICLE OUTPUT!
I'VE GOT THIS COVERED!
WE'VE GOT TO GET CLOSER!
NOT ONE STEP BACK!
(Surprised gasp)
WHAT THE?!
Pilot:
WE'RE BEING ATTACKED
FROM ANOTHER DIRECTION!
Feldt:
CHERUDIM HAS SHOT DOWN
AN ENEMY MACHINE!
Lasse:
ISN'T THIS GUY SUPPOSED
TO BE AN AMATEUR?
HMM.
Sumeragi:
WHAT IS HE?
YOU GOT HIM!
IT WAS JUST A LUCKY SHOT!
I CAN'T CLOSE IN!
HOW'S THE RESCUE COMING?
(Panting)
WHAT THE?!
(Rapid gunfire)
IT'S KATHARON.
I'LL HANDLE THINGS HERE.
GO AND SECURE E‐57,
LIEUTENANT!
THANKS!
Kati:
WHAT?
KATHARON IS RELEASING
THE PRISONERS?
DOES THIS MEAN
THEY'RE CONSPIRING
WITH CELESTIAL BEING?
(Startled gasp)
WHAT IN THE WORLD'S GOING ON?
(Surprised gasp)
SETSUNA,
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
GO TO THAT POINT.
ARIOS IS ON ITS WAY.
WHAT'S ARIOS?
THE NAME OF YOUR NEW GUNDAM.
HMM.
WE HAVE FOUND ALLELUJAH!
(Grunts)
LAUNCH ARIOS!
Mileina:
YOU GOT IT!
ARIOS, LAUNCHING!
PTOLEMY, RE‐SUBMERGING!
Lasse:
WHILE HOLDING THEM OFF
WITH GN MISSILES,
WE'LL MAKE OUR WAY
TO THE RENDEZVOUS POINT.
ONLY 120 SECONDS LEFT.
(Panting)
Allelujah:
THEY'RE RELEASING
THE OTHER PRISONERS, TOO.
BUT IT'S NOT SETSUNA'S DOING.
WHO ARE THOSE PEOPLE?
(Gasps)
THIS IS THE DESIGNATED POINT.
GUNDAM.
HOLD IT!
HUH?
END OF THE LINE!
DON'T MOVE, SUBJECT E‐57.
Marina:
(Gasping)
IS THERE A BATTLE
GOING ON OUTSIDE?
WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
Setsuna:
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
MOVE AWAY FROM THE DOOR!
WHAT?
GET BACK!
(Nervous gasp)
(Startled cry)
(Door opens)
HUH?
LET'S GO.
(Gasp)
SETSUNA!
(Shots being fired)
THERE'S LESS THAN
30 SECONDS LEFT!
MARIE.
STOP RIGHT THERE!
MARIE!
I'VE ALREADY TOLD YOU,
THAT'S NOT MY NAME!
NO, I'M MORE CERTAIN
THAN EVER THAT
THAT'S YOUR REAL NAME.
MARIE.
MARIE PARFACY.
M‐MARIE...
PARFACY?
Young Allelujah:
MARIE! MARIE!
(Peries gasps)
(Stunned gasp)
WHAT...
WHAT WAS...
THAT VISION I JUST HAD?
MARIE!
(Grunts)
GIVE YOURSELF UP, E‐57!
LIEUTENANT!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
(Frustrated grunt)
Tieria:
SETSUNA! ALLELUJAH!
WE'RE OUT OF TIME!
Setsuna:
ROGER!
DAMN IT.
MARIE IS RIGHT THERE
IN FRONT OF ME!
Tieria:
ALLELUJAH, WHAT'S WRONG?!
ALLELUJAH! ALLELUJAH!
(Frustrated growl)
ROGER.
(Gunshots)
MARIE.
ONE DAY I WILL COME BACK
FOR YOU.
I SWEAR!
Pilot:
TH‐THERE ARE THREE GUNDAMS!
AW, CRAP!
DAMN IT!
Kati:
CEASE FIRING!
DO WE FOLLOW THEM, MA'AM?
NO, SECURING THE FACILITY
COMES FIRST.
MA'AM.
(Growls)
Feldt:
THE GUNDAMS HAVE ESCAPED,
WE'RE COMMENCING
WITHDRAWAL NOW.
(Relieved sigh)
Haro:
MISSION COMPLETE!
(Relieved sigh)
THEY MANAGED TO GET AWAY.
Katharon Leader:
WE HAVE SUCCESSFULLY RESCUED
OUR COMRADES!
AND IT'S ALL THANKS
TO THE INFO FROM JEAN ONE!
YEAH, HE REALLY
CAME THROUGH FOR US!
HMM.
SHIRIN.
I JUST HEARD A MISSION REPORT
FROM ONE OF THE MEMBERS
OF THE RESCUE PARTY.
WHAT IS IT?
IT SEEMS WHEN THEY WERE IN
THE DETENTION CENTER,
THEY RECOGNIZED
A PRISONER THERE.
THE PRINCESS ROYAL
OF AZADISTAN,
MARINA ISMAIL.
WHAT? M‐MARINA?!
SHE WAS BEING HELD
IN DETENTION?!
IT SEEMS SO.
WHERE IS SHE?
I'M SORRY.
SHE ISN'T AMONG THE PEOPLE
WE TOOK OUT OF THERE.
(Worried)
OH, NO.
BUT ACCORDING TO THE REPORT,
PRINCESS MARINA WAS TAKEN AWAY
BY SOMEONE
WHO SEEMED TO BE
A MEMBER OF CELESTIAL BEING.
TAKEN AWAY?
A MEMBER OF CELESTIAL BEING?
(Gasps)
COULD IT BE HIM?
Shirin:
MARINA.
♪
(Sonar beeping)
HMM?
OH, THANKS,
TIERIA.
ALLELUJAH,
WHY WAS THE FEDERATION
GOVERNMENT HOLDING YOU?
THE SUPER SOLDIER
DATA WAS‐‐
MAN OH MAN,
THIS SHIP IS AMAZING!
Lyle:
IT EVEN OPERATES UNDERWATER!
L‐LOCKON!
BUT HOW?!
I'M GETTING TIRED OF
THAT REACTION.
UHH, I'M...
I'M SORRY.
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED.
YOU'RE STILL THE SAME.
YOU THINK SO?
THERE'S REALLY
NO NEED FOR YOU TO CHANGE.
WELCOME BACK,
ALLELUJAH.
HMM.
THANKS.
GOOD TO BE BACK.
Setsuna:
I GOT YOU INTO TROUBLE,
AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE
I APPROACHED YOU.
I'M SORRY, MARINA.
SETSUNA, WHY?
WHY HAVE YOU DECIDED TO
START FIGHTING AGAIN?
IT'S ALL I KNOW
HOW TO DO.
THAT'S NOT TRUE!
THERE ARE COUNTLESS WAYS
YOU CAN LIVE YOUR LIFE
WITHOUT HAVING TO
FIGHT AGAIN!
I CAN'T THINK OF ANY.
(Gasps)
THAT'S WHY MY WISH
WILL ONLY COME TRUE
THROUGH FIGHTING.
THAT'S JUST...
THAT'S JUST SO SAD.
WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
(Sobs)
I'M CRYING BECAUSE
YOU CAN'T.
Narrator:
THOSE WHO HAVE MADE MISTAKES
CAN ONLY CORRECT
THEIR MISTAKES THEMSELVES.
THE JOURNEY OF ATONEMENT
IS A JOURNEY OF REBIRTH.
NEXT EPISODE:
"A REASON TO FIGHT".
HOWEVER,
SINS NEVER DISAPPEAR.