Billy Katagiri:
I READ YOUR GRADUATION THESIS
ON THE TACTICAL THEORY
AND ANTICIPATED CASUALTIES
OF UNMANNED UNIT COMBAT.
SO, ARE YOU THINKING
OF PURSUING A CAREER
AS A TACTICAL FORECASTER
AFTER YOU GRADUATE?
THAT'S WHAT
I'D LIKE TO BE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
Billy:
I'M GONNA STAY IN COLLEGE
AND KEEP RESEARCHING
MOBILE SUITS
WITH PROFESSOR EIFMAN.
BUT YOU'RE
SIMPLY AMAZING!
YOU'RE ONLY 17 YEARS OLD,
AND ALREADY GRADUATING
FROM A PLACE LIKE THIS!
I STILL HAVE
A LOT OF THINGS TO LEARN.
I DON'T EVEN COME CLOSE
TO KATI.
KATI?
AH RIGHT, SHE'S
THE GENIUS TACTICIAN.
HER BRILLIANT SERIES OF
TACTICAL INSIGHTS
HAVE LED TO
VICTORY IN SEVEN CONFLICTS.
I HEAR THE AEU IS
SCOUTING HER
AND WANTS TO MAKE HER
A FIELD OFFICER.
THAT'S MY PERSONAL GOAL.
IF WARS CAN'T BE STOPPED,
THEN I'LL COME UP WITH TACTICS
TO RESOLVE THEM QUICKLY.
BY LIMITING CASUALTIES
TO A MINIMUM,
I'LL BE SAVING LIVES.
I WANT TO BECOME
A TACTICAL FORECASTER,
JUST LIKE KATI.
IF ANYONE CAN DO IT,
YOU CAN.
[GIGGLES]
WE MAY NEVER
SEE EACH OTHER AGAIN.
I'M GONNA BE LONELY.
YOU KNOW,
THAT'S NOT THE KIND OF THING
YOU SHOULD SAY TO A GIRL
WHO'S FIVE YEARS
YOUNGER THAN YOU.
UGH!
UH, WELL, IT'S JUST...
I GUESS NOT.
LEESA! I READ
YOUR GRADUATION THESIS.
YOU DID A GREAT JOB.
OH, THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
KATI!
THE NEXT TIME WE MEET
WE COULD BE ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
THOUGH, I'D HATE TO
FIND MYSELF
FACING YOU AS AN ENEMY.
Sumeragi: (Thinking)
MANNEQUIN.
WHY ARE YOU WITH THE A‐LAWS?
WHY?
♪
Kim:
COLONEL, ANY MOVEMENT
FROM SUILLE, YET?
NO, NO CHANGE IN THE SITUATION.
BUT TRUST ME, IT'S BOUND TO
MAKE A MOVE SOONER OR LATER.
SUILLE OPPOSES THE MIDDLE EAST
REORGANIZATION PLAN
AND WE CAN NOT
UNDERESTIMATE IT.
IF IT DECIDES TO TAKE ACTION
YOU CAN BE SURE OTHER COUNTRIES
WILL FOLLOW ITS LEAD.
TO PREVENT THAT FROM OCCURRING,
THE FEDERATION GOVERNMENT HAS
DECIDED TO DISPATCH
THE AUTONOMOUS
PEACEKEEPING FORCE.
SENDING THE A‐LAWS?
Manager:
THE FEDERATION FORCES HAVE
STATIONED TROOPS
ON SUILLE'S
NATIONAL BORDERS.
OBVIOUSLY, THEY'RE SENDING
A CLEAR WARNING TO SUILLE.
KNOWING ITS KING,
I DON'T EXPECT SUILLE
TO OPEN NEGOTIATIONS WITH
THE FEDERATION.
AND THE FACT
THE COMMUNICATIONS NETWORK
IN THE MIDDLE EAST
HAS BEEN CUT OFF,
MEANS ITS WORLD CLASS
INFORMATION INDUSTRY
CAN'T BE USED AS A WEAPON.
AND WITH THE FEDERATION
CONTROLLING WHAT'S HEARD,
IT'LL BE HARDER THAN EVER
FOR THE OUTSIDE WORLD
TO KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING.
WHAT'S SUILLE'S
MILITARY STRENGTH?
THOUGH I DON'T KNOW
ALL THE DETAILS,
I UNDERSTAND THEY ARE
THE STRONGEST COUNTRY
IN THE MIDDLE EAST.
RARE MINERAL DEPOSITS
AND ITS INFORMATION
INDUSTRY MADE IT
THE REGION'S RICHEST NATION
BEFORE THE FEDERATION
WAS FORMED.
HOW RECKLESS.
EVEN WITH THAT THEY'RE NO MATCH
FOR THE FEDERATION'S MILITARY.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT, THERE.
IN JUST FOUR YEARS,
EVEN A NATION LIKE SUILLE
COULDN'T HAVE DEVELOPED
NEW WEAPONS
TO SURPASS THOSE
OF THE FEDERATION.
HOWEVER, USING
OUR FORCES TO HELP THEM
ISN'T GOING TO MAKE
A DIFFERENCE.
THERE'S REALLY
ONLY ONE THING WE CAN DO.
WE'LL USE SUILLE'S INFORMATION.
WE'LL TAKE WHAT IT KNOWS
ABOUT THE FEDERATION'S ABUSES
IN THE MIDDLE EAST
AND USE KATHARON'S CONNECTIONS
TO SHOW THEM TO THE WHOLE WORLD.
IF PUBLIC OPINION OPPOSES
THE FEDERATION'S ACTIONS,
IT'LL HAVE TO STOP MEDDLING
IN THE MIDDLE EAST.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
THAT MEANS WE HAVE TO START
SOME KIND OF DIALOGUE
WITH SUILLE.
IKEDA, CAN YOU GET US IN TOUCH
WITH THE ROYAL FAMILY?
I'LL HAVE TO USE
MY CONNECTIONS
FROM WHEN I WAS A REPORTER,
BUT I SHOULD BE ABLE TO.
PLEASE, DO SO.
FOR THE MIDDLE EAST...
NO, FOR THE SAKE OF THE WORLD.
HMM.
I UNDERSTAND.
(Children talking)
HMM.
(Gasps)
SHIRIN.
WHAT'S THE SITUATION
IN AZADISTAN?
HOW ARE THE PEOPLE
FARING THESE DAYS?
THERE HASN'T BEEN ANY
SUBSTANTIAL NEWS
SINCE THE ANNOUNCEMENT ABOUT
THE PROVISIONAL GOVERNMENT
TAKING OVER.
INFORMATION ON
OUR COUNTRY IS ONLY RELEASED
AT THE WHIM OF THE FEDERATION.
AND EVEN IF WE WANTED
TO GO CHECK OUT
WHAT'S HAPPENING IN
AZADISTAN,
THE FEDERATION MILITARY HAS
SEALED THE BORDERS.
IT SEEMS HOPELESS.
I SEE.
MARINA.
IF WE EVER WANT TO
REBUILD AZADISTAN,
WE HAVE TO DEFEAT
THE FEDERATION.
YOU HAVE TO FIGHT.
AS THE PRINCESS,
YOU ARE OBLIGATED TO DO SO!
I CAN'T.
FIGHTING ONLY BRINGS
MORE FIGHTING!
IF I RECLAIMED AZADISTAN
BY FORCE,
DO YOU ACTUALLY THINK
THAT WOULD BRING
HAPPINESS TO EVERYONE?
SO WE SHOULD
JUST GRIN AND BEAR IT?!
ARE YOU FORGETTING OUR HOMELAND
WAS STOLEN FROM US?!
SHIRIN.
I JUST THINK...
(Sighs)
Shirin:
FINE, THEN.
YOU JUST CONTINUE DOING NOTHING
LIKE YOU'RE DOING NOW.
I AM GOING TO FIGHT.
BECAUSE IF I DON'T,
WE'LL NEVER GET
OUR COUNTRY BACK.
SETSUNA.
I UNDERSTAND NOW.
HOW YOU MUST HAVE FELT WHEN
YOU LOST YOUR HOMELAND, KRUGIS.
IT FEELS LIKE
THE VERY GROUND IS DISAPPEARING
FROM BENEATH MY FEET.
HOW ARE YOU ABLE TO FIGHT
WHEN YOU FEEL LIKE THIS?
Goodman:
ACCORDING TO THE REPORT FROM
OUR OBSERVATION TEAM,
THERE'S A STRONG PROBABILITY
THAT CELESTIAL BEING'S
SPACESHIP
IS HEADED TO LAGRANGE THREE.
SINCE MAJOR RINDT IS
ON ANOTHER MISSION,
I'M LEAVING YOU IN CHARGE
OF THE GUNDAM PURSUIT.
SIR.
I'M SENDING YOU REINFORCEMENTS.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU TO AVENGE
THE LOSS OF COLONEL ZHEJIANG.
(Sighs)
KUJO.
Sumeragi: (Weeping)
EMILIO!
Kati:
IS IT POSSIBLE
THE MEMORY OF THAT INCIDENT
LINGERED WITHIN HER,
AND SO SHE DEVOTED HERSELF
TO CELESTIAL BEING'S
IDEAL OF
ELIMINATING WAR?
IT'S CRAZY.
IT'S NOTHING
BUT A FOOLISH DREAM.
THERE'S NO WAY THE WORLD
WILL EVER BE FREE OF CONFLICT.
AND WASN'T THE REASON
WE BECAME TACTICAL FORECASTERS
SO WE COULD PREVENT
THOSE CONFLICTS
FROM DRAGGING ON?
I'VE GOT YOUR MEAL HERE,
COLONEL, NICE AND HOT!
DIDN'T ANYONE
TEACH YOU TO KNOCK?!
(Frightened yelp)
BRING'S BEEN GIVEN ORDERS
TO LAUNCH AN ATTACK.
(Pleased sigh)
HOW WILL YOU REACT,
CELESTIAL BEING?
(Metal grinding)
SENSORS ARE
INDICATING ALL GREEN.
PARTICLE SUPPLY LEVELS
READING SATISFACTORY.
(Shocked gasp)
AZADISTAN IS...
BUT MY COUNTRY IS...
Setsuna: (Thinking)
MARINA.
ALI AL‐SAACHEZ.
NOTHING HAS CHANGED.
AND I STILL HAVEN'T BEEN
ABLE TO...
Feldt:
E‐SENSORS HAVE
DETECTED SOMETHING!
ENEMY MACHINE CLOSING IN!
AN ENEMY?!
IS IT A‐LAWS?!
(Gasps)
IT'S COMING.
HUH?
WHAT'S THE MATTER, MARIE?
(Grunts in pain)
MARIE!
IT'S COMING.
SOMETHING
THAT'S DANGEROUS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
DANGEROUS?
Feldt:
THE MACHINE IS APPROACHING
AT A RATE OF 78 KILO‐SECONDS!
WHAT KIND OF SPEED
DOES IT HAVE?!
THE ENEMY FORCE
IS ONLY ONE MACHINE?
Mileina:
ARIOS AND SERAVEE ARE
STILL BEING REPAIRED!
GUNDAMS, EMERGENCY LAUNCH!
INTERCEPT THE ENEMY MACHINE.
Setsuna:
00, LAUNCHING FIRST.
THAT'S IT.
IT'S EQUIPPED WITH
A PSEUDO SOLAR REACTOR.
Setsuna:
IT'S A‐LAWS, LIKE I THOUGHT!
IT'S SO MANEUVERABLE.
ANOTHER NEW MODEL?
HUH?!
THAT'S A‐‐
IT HAS A GN FIELD!
THE FEDERATION HAS MACHINES
THAT USE FIELDS?!
(Grunts)
(Surprised gasp)
(Stunned gasp)
(Grunts)
I NEED THE TRANS‐AM!
(Startled gasp)
Lyle:
SETSUNA, YOU ALL RIGHT?!
THAT NEW MODEL WAS
STRONG ENOUGH TO OVERPOWER 00?!
Lyle:
WHAT THE...?
IT RAN AWAY?
Feldt:
THE ENEMY IS WITHDRAWING!
WELL, THAT WAS
A PRETTY QUICK BATTLE.
AFTER THE GUNDAMS ARE
SAFELY ON BOARD,
HEAD FOR LAGRANGE THREE
AT TOP SPEED.
Feldt:
ROGER THAT.
SO WHAT EXACTLY WAS
THE POINT OF ALL THAT?
THEY'RE TELLING US THAT
THEY CAN DEPLOY FORCES
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE,
AND THEY WANT TO SHOW US
THE CAPABILITIES OF
THEIR NEW MODEL.
IT'S A CHECK AND A WARNING.
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL BE NEEDING
THE 0‐RAISER'S HELP NOW
MORE THAN EVER.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
WAS THIS ANOTHER OF
MANNEQUIN'S FEINTS?
THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
THE PILOT OF THAT NEW MODEL
IS AN INNOVATOR.
THE ONE THAT TOOK CONTROL
OF VEDA IS BEHIND THIS.
HE COULD DEVELOP SUITS
THAT CAN ALSO USE GN FIELDS.
AND THAT MEANS...
Sumeragi:
TIERIA?
(Gasps)
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
UH, NO.
WHY AM I NOT TELLING THEM
ABOUT HIM?
WHY AM I STILL HESITATING?
Goodman:
MAJOR RINDT,
HOW ARE THINGS
PROGRESSING?
EXACTLY AS PLANNED.
SO FAR, THINGS ARE PROCEEDING
WITHOUT A HITCH.
REPORT BACK TO ME
WHEN EVERYTHING'S IN PLACE.
AT THAT POINT I WILL BE
TAKING DIRECT COMMAND.
MESSAGE UNDERSTOOD, SIR.
JUST YOU WAIT, THOSE OF YOU
WHO OPPOSE
THE UNITED GOVERNMENT.
YOU ARE ABOUT TO HAVE A TASTE
OF HEAVEN'S THUNDER.
THE JUDGMENT OF GOD.
Feldt:
OPEN HATCH.
Mileina:
PTOLEMY HAS ALIGNED WITH
LASER SENSORS.
PTOLEMY, TOUCHING DOWN IN
THREE, TWO, ONE.
DOCKING COMPLETE.
Feldt:
ATTACHING ANCHOR ARMS.
CONNECTING BOARDING HATCH.
(Surprised gasp)
HEY, WE'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR YOU GUYS TO SHOW UP!
HI, MOM!
I'M BACK HOME!
SO, HAVE YOU BEEN ALL RIGHT,
MILEINA?
OF COURSE I HAVE!
SHE SAID, "MOM" JUST NOW,
DIDN'T SHE?
YES, SHE DID.
SO, THAT MEANS...
OH, RIGHT, I FORGOT.
SOME OF YOU ARE MEETING HER
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
THIS IS MY WIFE.
HELLO, I'M LINDA VASHTI.
WHOA, SHE'S YOUNG!
THERE OUGHT TO BE A LAW.
HEY, WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?!
LET'S PUT THE JOKING
ASIDE FOR NOW.
WHY DO YOU THINK
THIS IS A JOKE?!
HOW LONG TO RESUPPLY AND
REPAIR PTOLEMY AND THE GUNDAMS?
HUH?
WHAT HAPPENED OUT THERE?
THE A‐LAWS ARE CONDUCTING
OPERATIONS IN THIS SECTOR.
WELL, EVEN THOUGH
I THINK
OUR CAMOUFLAGE HERE
IS PERFECT...
I UNDERSTAND.
Anew:
HOWEVER,
REPAIR AND RESUPPLY WILL
REQUIRE AT LEAST FIVE DAYS.
AND WHO ARE YOU?
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU BEFORE.
PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
I WAS SCOUTED WHEN CELESTIAL
BEING RESUMED ITS OPERATIONS.
MY NAME IS ANEW RETURNER.
YOU WERE SCOUTED?
WELL, WHO SCOUTED YOU?
Ian:
WANG LIU MEI
INTRODUCED HER TO US.
ANEW IS SIMPLY AMAZING!
SHE'S AN EXPERT IN ASTROPHYSICS,
MOBILE SUIT ENGINEERING,
AND REGENERATION TREATMENTS.
SHE CAN NAVIGATE AND COOK,
AND TO TOP IT OFF,
SHE'S GORGEOUS!
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
IS SHE A KEEPER OR WHAT?!
I LOOK FORWARD TO
WORKING WITH ALL OF YOU.
WE'VE RECEIVED
A CODED MESSAGE FROM IKEDA!
THE SUILLE ROYAL FAMILY
WANTS A CONFERENCE.
REALLY? HE GOT THROUGH
TO THEM!
I'LL REPRESENT US
AT THE CONFERENCE.
YOU'LL BE IN CHARGE
WHILE I'M GONE.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THINGS HERE.
YOU SHOULD TAKE
AN ESCORT WITH YOU
TO BE ON THE SAFE SIDE.
MM‐HMM.
I PLAN TO.
THIS CAR HERE IS RED.
HEY, PRINCESS?
YES, DEAR?
I HEARD SUILLE'S GONNA BE
ATTACKED, IS IT TRUE?
(Startled gasp)
NOW, NOW, STOP BOTHERING
THE PRINCESS!
I'M VERY SORRY.
THE BOY IS FROM SUILLE,
AND HE'S WORRIED ABOUT
WHAT COULD HAPPEN.
HMM.
WHY DON'T PEOPLE JUST
GET ALONG WITH EACH OTHER?
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN,
I WONDER THE SAME THING.
SO WE HAVE TO DO OUR BEST
TO THINK UP WAYS FOR PEOPLE
TO GET ALONG.
THEY SHOULD JUST SIT DOWN
AND HAVE A MEAL TOGETHER!
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
I KNOW!
(Giggles)
THAT WAS GOOD.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU THINK
PEOPLE SHOULD DO?
HMM...
EVERYONE CAN PLAY TOGETHER,
SING SONGS TOGETHER,
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND SHOW EACH OTHER
THEIR COOL STUFF!
AND THEN ALSO,
THEY CAN... UM... UM...
(Chuckles)
SO THIS IS THE 0‐RAISER.
THIS MACHINE INCORPORATES
SPECIAL FUNCTIONS
THAT HELP YOU CONTROL
THE TWIN DRIVE SYSTEM.
AND IT AMPLIFIES THE TRANS‐AM.
AND THAT MACHINE?
Anew:
A SUPPORT UNIT FOR ARIOS,
THE GN ARCHER.
LET'S START TESTING IT,
SETSUNA.
ROGER THAT.
WHO WOULD'VE THOUGHT
THERE'D BE A BASE THIS LARGE
AT LAGRANGE THREE?
HMM?
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
HMM.
I'M KIND OF AT A LOSS ABOUT
WHAT I SHOULD DO.
BECAUSE OF SOMETHING I DID,
A LOT OF PEOPLE
LOST THEIR LIVES.
SOMEHOW I HAVE TO
MAKE UP FOR THAT.
BUT IF IT MEANS HAVING TO FIGHT,
OR TO ACTUALLY KILL PEOPLE,
I COULDN'T POSSIBLY‐‐
IT'S ONLY NATURAL
THAT YOU CAN'T DO IT.
YES, BUT...
I HAVE TO HELP OUT SOMEHOW.
THERE MUST BE
SOMETHING I CAN DO.
UM, CAN I ASK YOU
SOMETHING?
SURE, WHAT ABOUT?
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
IF YOU INTEND TO STAY WITH THEM
FROM NOW ON.
YES. AS LONG AS
ALLELUJAH IS HERE.
EVEN IF IT MEANS
YOU MAY HAVE TO FIGHT?
I USED TO BE A SOLDIER,
SO I BELIEVE
I'VE ALREADY MADE MY PEACE
WITH THAT POSSIBILITY.
BESIDES,
I'VE MADE MY CHOICE.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS, I WILL
NEVER LEAVE ALLELUJAH AGAIN.
HOW I ENVY YOU.
THERE'S SOMEONE I FEEL
THAT WAY ABOUT, TOO.
IF, BY SOME CHANCE, WE WERE TO
SEE EACH OTHER AGAIN,
I DON'T THINK
I'D LEAVE HER SIDE EITHER.
BUT I'M WORRIED.
(Groaning in pain)
Saji:
I'M REALLY WORRIED.
(Gasping and moaning)
A RENDEZVOUS IN SPACE
JUST TO ADD MORE PERSONNEL.
HEY!
ANOTHER NEW MODEL.
COLONEL!
NEW MODEL?!
I WANT ONE,
GIVE ME A NEW MODEL TOO!
SHUT UP!
(Frightened gasp)
BUT... BUT COLONEL!
I NEVER EXPECTED YOU TO
JOIN THE A‐LAWS, TOO.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO BRING THIS ABOUT?
A MAN OF FEW WORDS,
AS ALWAYS.
WE'RE USING
THE MEMENTO MORI.
THE MEMENTO MORI?
IS THAT SO?
FINALLY, RIBBONS.
Regene:
USING THE MEMENTO MORI.
Ribbons:
WITH THIS, THE MIDDLE EAST PLAN
WILL ACCELERATE,
AND WE SHALL UNITE
THE WILL OF HUMANITY.
BY UNITE,
DON'T YOU ACTUALLY MEAN
TO SAY "STANDARDIZE"?
NO, I MEAN UNITE.
IN THE SENSE THAT THEY WILL
UNITE BEFORE OUR FEET.
I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR YOUR HELP IN BUILDING
THE MEMENTO MORI.
I HAVE GREAT HOPES
FOR THE FUTURE
YOU INNOVATORS ARE CREATING.
Al‐Saachez:
WHATCHA DOING?
(Surprised gasp)
YO!
Nena:
IT'S YOU!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO...
MICHAEL AND JOHANN WERE...
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO KILLED MY BROTHERS!
GET OUT OF HERE!
I THOUGHT YOU LOOKED FAMILIAR,
YOU WERE THAT LITTLE GIRL.
BUT CLEARLY YOU'VE BECOME
A WOMAN SINCE.
SON OF A‐‐
(Gasps)
YOU WANNA FIGHT ME?
BETTER THINK AGAIN.
YOU WERE LUCKY TO
KEEP YOUR LIFE LAST TIME.
WHY THROW IT AWAY NOW?
(Grunts)
(Angry growl)
Mileina:
0 RAISER AND 00'S DOCKING
IS COMPLETE!
ALL LINKAGES READING
SATISFACTORY!
ALL RIGHT, SETSUNA,
WE'RE GONNA TEST
0 RAISER'S CONTROL SYSTEM.
LET'S START UP TRANS‐AM!
ROGER THAT!
Operator #1:
TRANSFORMATION TO
STRAFING MODE COMPLETE.
Operator #2:
POWER SUPPLY AT 98%.
Operator #3:
OUTPUT SET AT 6800.
Operator #4:
TARGET POINT
ERROR CORRECTION COMPLETE.
Operator #1:
STRAFING OUTPUT SECTION
REPORTING NO PROBLEMS.
WELL, GENERAL,
STRAFING PREPARATIONS
ARE NOW COMPLETE.
VERY WELL, YOU MAY
COMMENCE THE COUNTDOWN.
COMMENCE FINAL COUNTDOWN!
Operator #2:
ROGER.
COUNTING DOWN TO FIRING.
TEN, NINE,
I LOOKED AROUND
LIKE YOU ORDERED, BOSS,
BUT I COULDN'T FIND ANYONE
MATCHING THE DESCRIPTION.
IS THAT SO?
THEN THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH.
SORRY TO
WASTE YOUR TIME.
DON'T FORGET THAT
YOU'RE MY CLIENT, BOSS.
YOU'RE FREE TO USE ME
AS YOU PLEASE.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE I HAVE SOMETHING
THAT'LL MAKE UP FOR IT.
YOU SHOULD WATCH THIS TOO.
WHAT IS IT?
SOMETHING I THINK
YOU'RE GOING TO ENJOY.
TIME UNTIL TRANS‐AM STARTUP.
EIGHT, SEVEN, SIX, FIVE, FOUR,
THREE, TWO, ONE.
Operator #2:
COMMENCE STRAFING.
(Panicked gasping and muttering)
(Screaming)
(Gasping)
WH‐WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT THE...?!
♪
Anew:
TIME UNTIL TRANS‐AM STARTUP.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE,
TWO, ONE.
SETSUNA!
ROGER!
ACTIVATING TRANS‐AM!
TOPOLOGICAL DEFECT SHIFTING
TO HIGHER LEVEL.
WE'RE GETTING AN INCREASE
IN BOTH PARTICLE GENERATION
AND EMISSION RATES!
IT'S PASSING
THE NORMAL 180% FIGURE,
AND THE NUMBERS ARE
STILL CLIMBING!
IT'S LOOKING GOOD, LINDA!
OH, YES!
Anew:
230. 260.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
IT JUST BROKE 290%!
IT WHAT?
ABOUT TO EXCEED
THEORETICAL LIMIT!
BUT THAT'S...
THEN THIS IS...
THE TWIN DRIVE
THAT AEOLIA ENVISIONED.
ARE WE SEEING ITS TRUE POWER?
(Startled gasp)
COLONEL!
HUH?
(Cries)
MY HEAD!
(Grunts in pain)
WHA... WHAT IS THIS...
FEELING?
THAT LIGHT,
IT COULDN'T BE!
(Grunts)
Peries:
COLONEL!
GET AWAY FROM THERE, COLONEL!
RUN, COLONEL!
Hallelujah:
THE QUANTUM PARTICLES ARE
ACCELERATING IN THIS DIRECTION.
DAMN.
GUESS IT'S ABOUT TIME I WOKE UP.
Narrator:
WITH ITS TRUE AWAKENING,
THANKS TO 00 RAISER.
THE TWIN DRIVE INVITES SETSUNA
INTO UNKNOWN TERRITORY.
NEXT EPISODE: "00'S VOICE".
IS IT THE BIRTH CRY
OF A NEW WORLD?