WHY...
WHY DO YOU...
LOOK JUST LIKE ME?
IT'S BECAUSE WE HAVE THE
EXACT SAME DNA.
BASE SEQUENCE PATTERN...
0988 TYPE.
THAT MEANS...
YOU ARE...
AN INNOVATOR.
REGENE REGETTA.
YOU'RE AN INNOVATOR!
THAT'S RIGHT.
HIS VOICE IS IN MY HEAD!
(Telepathically)
THIS IS A TELEPATHIC ABILITY
USING QUANTUM BRAINWAVES,
CATALYZED BY GN PARTICLES.
WE USE THEM TO PROVIDE US
WITH A DIRECT LINK TO VEDA.
AND THANKS TO GENETIC
MANIPULATION AND NANOMACHINES,
WE DO NOT AGE.
BEINGS LIKE US ARE ESSENTIAL
TO AEOLIA SCHENBERG'S PLAN.
(Sighs)
DON'T TELL ME...
YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT THERE WERE
OTHERS LIKE YOU?
(Angry breath)
(Chuckling) BECAUSE
YOU'RE A GUNDAM MEISTER,
IT SEEMS VEDA
MUST HAVE PLACED
RESTRICTIONS ON WHAT YOU
WERE ALLOWED TO ACCESS.
THAT CAN'T BE...
IN THAT CASE,
LET ME ENLIGHTEN YOU...
STAGE ONE OF THE PLAN WAS
TO HAVE CELESTIAL BEING
USE ARMED INTERVENTIONS
TO TRIGGER
A UNIFICATION OF THE WORLD.
STAGE TWO
IS TO USE THE A‐LAWS
TO UNITE THE WILL OF
ALL MANKIND.
AND STAGE THREE IS TO PUSH
HUMANITY INTO OUTER SPACE
AND PREPARE THEM FOR THE
DIALOGUES THAT ARE TO COME.
THAT IS AEOLIA'S PLAN
IN ITS ENTIRETY.
YES. WE WHO ARE ADAPTED
TO THE ENVIRONMENT OF SPACE...
ARE TO GUIDE HUMANITY UP AND
ONWARD TO AN ALL‐NEW FRONTIER.
(Gasping)
HONESTLY.
THAT WAS UNNECESSARY.
♪
Ian:
DAMN THAT ALLELUJAH...
DAMAGING HIS MACHINE RIGHT
AFTER SETSUNA WRECKED HIS...
AND WHAT'S THIS I HEAR
ABOUT HIM BRINGING
A GIRLFRIEND BACK WITH HIM?
I MEAN, REALLY.
A GIRLFRIEND...
FEELING LONELY, SAJI?
HMM?
I GUESS SO.
A LITTLE BIT.
Lasse:
THAT GIRL, MARIE. SHE'S FROM THE
SUPERHUMAN INSTITUTE, RIGHT?
DO YOU THINK IT'S SAFE LETTING
HER ON BOARD THE SHIP?
WELL, WE RAN A PRETTY
THOROUGH CHECK ON HER.
BESIDES...
I THINK ALLELUJAH NEEDS HER.
WHY'S THAT?
Sumeragi:
HE NEEDS A REASON TO FIGHT.
QUICK QUESTION
FOR YOU GUYS:
ARE YOU TWO
LOVERS OR WHAT?
(Both gasping)
(Screaming)
MY FEMALE INTUITION
GOT IT RIGHT!
(Sighing)
SO KLAUS AND THE OTHERS
MANAGED TO GET AWAY SAFELY.
AND YET...
"FEDERATION TO LEAD
MIDDLE EAST RENEWAL PLAN.
AZADISTAN DISSOLVED."
MARINA ISMAIL...
Leanne:
PRINCESS MARINA...
HMM?
WELL, HELLO THERE...
TRY TO CHEER UP.
I'LL EVEN GIVE YOU THIS.
(Sighing)
THANK YOU,
LITTLE ONE...
THANK YOU.
REGENE REGETTA...
Regene:
IN ORDER TO GUIDE
HUMANITY TO A NEW STAGE...
A GREAT WAVE IS
NECESSARY.
(Gasps)
INDEED... A WAVE
CALLED REFORMATION.
(Sighing)
SO YOU'RE SAYING WE SHOULD JUST
LET THE A‐LAWS CONTINUE
THEIR DETESTABLE CONDUCT?
BUT REFORM
IS NEVER PAINLESS.
DO YOU THINK WHAT YOU'VE BEEN
DOING IS HARMLESS?
(Sighing)
YOU PEOPLE... HAVE BECOME
OBSTACLES TO AEOLIA'S PLAN.
(Gasping)
ALL OF US WERE CREATED FOR THE
SAKE OF THE PLAN.
THE REASON WHY WE EXIST
IS TO EXECUTE THE PLAN...
AND SEE IT THROUGH
TO ITS END.
YOU SHOULD KNOW...
YOU ARE CONTRADICTING THE REASON
FOR YOUR EXISTENCE.
(Stunned gasp)
(Splash)
TIERIA ERDE...
LET US GUIDE HUMANITY,
TOGETHER.
AS INNOVATORS,
HAND IN HAND.
NO NEED TO ANSWER NOW.
I'LL SEE YOU AGAIN.
BECAUSE YOU AND I...
ARE ALWAYS CONNECTED.
INNOVATORS...
THEY'RE THE ONES
WHO EXECUTE THE PLAN.
AND IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN I'LL HAVE TO CHOOSE
THE PATH OF‐‐
Lockon:
DON'T SQUEEZE YOURSELF INTO A
SPECIFIC MOLD LIKE THAT.
(Gasping)
JUST GO OUT THERE AND DO WHAT
YOU BELIEVE IS RIGHT...
AND BE AS GUNG‐HO
AS YOU WANT WHILE DOING IT.
I MEAN AFTER ALL...
OLD MAN AEOLIA ENTRUSTED THE
GUNDAMS TO US RIGHT?
LOCKON...
HUH?
Allelujah:
FELDT...
I HAVEN'T INTRODUCED
YOU TWO YET, HAVE I?
SHE'LL BE LIVING
ON PTOLEMY WITH US. THIS IS‐‐
SOMA PERIES.
HUH?
FOUR YEARS AGO
SHE FOUGHT AGAINST US
AS A PILOT
FOR THE UN FORCES.
YES, BUT FELDT...
IN THAT LAST BATTLE, WE LOST A
LOT OF GOOD PEOPLE...
LIKE CHRISTINA...
AND LICHTY...
DR. MORENO...
AND THEN...
WE LOST LOCKON, TOO!
I‐I DIDN'T‐‐
NOW HOLD ON
A MINUTE!
FELDT!
MARIE WASN'T‐‐
I KNOW THAT!
I KNOW IT WASN'T HER FAULT!
BUT...I JUST HAD TO SAY
SOMETHING!
FELDT!
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT, MARIE.
TO FELDT, ALL THE CREW
OF THIS SHIP
ARE LIKE
CLOSE FAMILY MEMBERS...
THIS SHIP IS...
EVERYTHING TO HER.
(Thinking)
LIEUTENANT PERIES
WAS KILLED IN BATTLE.
I KNOW COLONEL SMIRNOV
HIMSELF REPORTED IT BUT‐‐
Louise:
EXCUSE ME, MA'AM.
I HAVE A REQUEST, COLONEL.
I'D LIKE YOUR
PERMISSION TO BECOME
THE PILOT
OF THIS MACHINE.
A MERE WARRANT OFFICER
WANTS TO PILOT A CUSTOM AHEAD?
I WILL NOT DISAPPOINT
YOU IN BATTLE, MA'AM.
LET ME TAKE REVENGE
FOR THE LIEUTENANT!
DENIED.
I CANNOT APPROVE
YOUR REQUEST.
Rindt:
I DON'T SEE A PROBLEM!
I WILL PERSONALLY RECOMMEND
THAT GENERAL GOODMAN
APPROVES YOUR REQUEST.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, SIR!
AND PERHAPS
YOU COULD DO ME A FAVOR.
I HAVE A SPECIAL JOB
FOR YOU.
A JOB?
BUT, MAJOR,
THIS IS A...
FEEL FREE TO TAKE LIEUTENANT
SMIRNOV TO ACT AS YOUR ESCORT.
YOU DO REALIZE WHAT
SENDING OUT TWO PILOTS WILL DO
TO OUR
MOBILE SUIT FORCE?
OH, I'VE ALREADY ARRANGED FOR
SUBSTITUTE PILOTS.
AND THEY'LL BE BRINGING
THE LATEST MODEL,
EVEN MORE ADVANCED
THAN THE AHEAD.
WHAT?
OH, YES.
AND I UNDERSTAND THAT AMONG THE
REPLACEMENT PERSONNEL
IS A MAN
YOU KNOW QUITE WELL.
WHO WOULD'VE EVER IMAGINED THAT
I'D FIND MYSELF
JOINING THE A‐LAWS?
THAT MUST BE THE NEW MODEL
Patrick:
COLONEL!
HEY, I'VE COME BACK!
OH NO, IT'S HIM!
Spokesperson:
THE MIDDLE EAST
REORGANIZATION PLAN IS
THE HIGHEST CURRENT PRIORITY
OF THE EARTH SPHERE
FEDERATION GOVERNMENT,
IN ACCORDANCE WITH ITS GOAL
OF TOTAL UNIFICATION.
WE INTEND TO STABILIZE
RELIGIOUS AND ETHNIC CONFLICTS
BETWEEN NATIONS
BY USING THE FEDERATION FORCES
TO SECURE ALL
THE NATIONAL BORDERS.
AS FOR ALL CONTINUING
INTERNAL CONFLICTS
CONSIDERATION IS
BEING GIVEN TO RELOCATING
(Scoffing)
OH, COME ON,
THIS WOMAN IS SPOUTING SOME
RIDICULOUS STUFF HERE.
EVEN SO, THIS WILL PROBABLY GO
OVER WELL WITH THE PUBLIC.
WHY'S THAT?
BECAUSE IT DOESN'T
AFFECT THEM DIRECTLY.
Sumeragi:
WITH SOLAR POWER,
THE ORBITAL ELEVATOR PROJECT,
AND COLONY DEVELOPMENT,
THE FEDERATION HAS
ACHIEVED FINANCIAL STABILITY.
AS A RESULT OF THESE BLESSINGS,
THE STANDARD OF LIVING
FOR PEOPLE IN
THE FEDERATION HAS RISEN.
AND THE A‐LAWS
AND THE SECURITY AGENCY
ARE SUPPRESSING ALL
DISSIDENT ACTIVITY.
IF NOBODY ASKS QUESTIONS,
THERE'S NO HARM DONE.
THAT'S WHY THERE
WON'T BE ANY COMPLAINTS.
BUT EVEN WITH ALL THAT, THERE
ARE STILL PEOPLE OUT THERE
WHO ARE DYING
FOR NO GOOD REASON.
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT'S THE WAY
THE WORLD IS MEANT TO BE.
IT'S THE BASTARDS
WHO FOUNDED THE A‐LAWS.
THEY'RE THE MAIN CULPRITS.
Regene:
STAGE TWO IS TO USE THE A‐LAWS
TO UNITE THE WILL
OF ALL MANKIND.
INNOVATORS...
(Door slides open)
FELDT... I'M...
I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST HORRIBLE,
AREN'T I?
I ALWAYS INTEND
TO HANG TOUGH,
BUT I LET MYSELF BE SPOILED
BY HOW KIND EVERYONE IS.
DON'T WORRY,
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
AFTER ALL... WE'RE FAMILY.
(Gasping)
(Sighs)
DO YOU KNOW HOW
FOOLISH YOU ARE, LIEUTENANT?
I WARNED YOU NOT TO
GET INVOLVED WITH THE A‐LAWS!
I VOLUNTEERED FOR THE
A‐LAWS MYSELF!
BECAUSE I WANTED
TO PROTECT YOU, COLONEL!
(Sighing)
IF YOU STAY HERE...
EVENTUALLY YOU'LL HAVE TO
FIGHT THE GUNDAMS.
YOU'LL JUST END UP DEAD.
PARDON ME, BUT
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT, MA'AM,
I'VE SURVIVED SEVEN
BATTLES WITH THE GUNDAMS.
MY COMRADES GAVE ME
A NICKNAME, THEY CALL ME
"COLASOUR THE INDESTRUCTABLE".
DON'T YOU KNOW THEY'RE
DISPARAGING YOU?
HO‐HO! YOU REALLY THINK SO?
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT!
(Sighing)
YOU'RE HOPELESS.
IT'S NOT EASY
BEING POPULAR, IS IT?
HE REALLY IS HOPELESS.
Ian:
THE TEMPORARY REPAIRS TO 00 AND
ARIOS ARE ALL DONE.
AND SOME MORE GOOD NEWS:
TWO OF OUR SUPPORT MACHINES
ARE FINISHED.
TO GET THE TWIN DRIVE WORKING
JUST RIGHT, I'D LIKE TO
TAKE IT UP INTO SPACE FIRST
AND WORK ON FINE TUNING IT.
I UNDERSTAND.
MILEINA, DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN TAKE OVER
THE MAINTENANCE DUTIES FOR IAN?
YES, MA'AM!
Lasse:
WE HAVE A CODED MESSAGE
FROM WANG LIU MEI.
Sumeragi:
DECODE IT.
Liu Mei:
EVERYONE. I HAVE SOLID
INTELLIGENCE THAT MEMBERS
OF THE A‐LAWS LEADERSHIP
WHO HAVEN'T PREVIOUSLY APPEARED
IN PUBLIC WILL BE ATTENDING
AN EXCLUSIVE PARTY
I WILL REPORT
OUR FINDINGS LATER.
WAIT, I'M GOING TOO, I WANT TO
BE PART OF THE RECON MISSION.
BUT TIERIA...
I WANNA SEE OUR REAL ENEMY
WITH MY OWN TWO EYES.
OKAY, BUT THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
THE ENEMY KNOWS WHO WE ARE.
I'M WILLING
TO BE HIS BACKUP.
WELL, I GUESS
THERE'S NO CHOICE
BUT ONLY UNDER THE CONDITION YOU
FOLLOW MY EXACT INSTRUCTIONS.
WAS THAT ALL RIGHT?
YES. THAT WAS
BEAUTIFULLY DONE.
MS. FELDT.
I'M SORRY ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED.
MY EMOTIONS
GOT THE BEST OF ME.
IT'S FINE...
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
GOODBYE.
SO, YOU...
SO YOU REALLY
DO TREASURE
EVERYONE ON THIS SHIP,
DON'T YOU?
THAT'S BECAUSE...
THIS IS MY FAMILY.
I DIDN'T EXPECT THE PARTICLE
OUTPUT OF THE TWIN DRIVE
TO CAUSE THE MACHINE
TO SCREAM LIKE THAT...
BUT ONCE WE HAVE THE 0‐RAISER
WE CAN COVER THAT, TOO.
IN FACT, ONCE WE HAVE IT,
THIS MACHINE WILL SURPASS
ALL OTHER GUNDAMS.
(People laughing and chatting)
IT CERTAINLY WAS A
DELIGHTFUL AUCTION.
OH, HEY...
HUH?
OOH...
Guest 1:
IT'S WANG LIU MEI.
Guest 2:
SHE BECAME HEAD OF THE WANG
FAMILY WHEN SHE WAS ONLY 15.
Guest 3:
SHE IS STUNNING.
I WONDER WHERE THEY ARE?
(Gasping)
THAT WAS PROBABLY MISS
SUMERAGI'S IDEA...
MY MISTRESS...
LOOK THERE.
Liu Mei:
HOMER KATAGIRI.
HE'S THE HEAD OF DEVELOPMENT
FOR US A‐LAWS.
HELLO, I'M
BILLY KATAGIRI.
OH, SO YOU'RE COMMANDER
KATAGIRI'S NEPHEW...
I'VE HEARD YOU'RE
SOME KIND OF GENIUS.
NO, NOT EVEN CLOSE.
(All laughing)
Tieria:
THAT'S THE COMMANDER
OF THE A‐LAWS THERE.
BUT HE'S NOT THE ONE
CALLING THE SHOTS.
WHERE IS THE REAL ENEMY?
WHERE?
REGENE'S WILLFULNESS HAS PUT ME
IN A TOUGH SPOT.
I WOULD'VE PREFERRED
TO LET HIM ROAM FREELY
FOR JUST A WHILE LONGER.
SO UH... WHY DO YOU
NEED ME AT THIS PARTY?
YOU ARE THE HEAD
OF THE HALEVY FAMILY,
ONE OF A‐LAWS PRIMARY
SPONSORS.
ALL THE PEOPLE GATHERED HERE
TONIGHT ARE WORKING TO ACHIEVE
A PERMANENT PEACE BY
UNITING THIS WORLD OF OURS.
AND SO WE FIND OURSELVES
IN NEED OF THEIR COOPERATION.
OF COURSE, THIS IS ALSO TO
DEFEAT THE GUNDAMS.
WHEN I'M DONE GREETING
EVERYBODY,
MAY I BE EXCUSED
AND RETURN TO WORK?
CERTAINLY.
ALSO, TO COMPENSATE YOU FOR YOUR
TIME AND INCONVENIENCE,
I'VE ARRANGED TO HAVE
THE AHEAD THAT
SOMA PERIES USED TO PILOT
REASSIGNED FOR YOU TO USE.
I'M GRATEFUL, SIR.
DO YOU KNOW
ANY OF THESE VIPS?
THEY'RE JUST
ACQUAINTANCES.
HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
UH, NO...
IT'S NOTHING.
(Party guests mingling)
WOW THAT SOUNDS
LIKE A GREAT HOBBY!
THANK YOU
FOR SAYING SO.
I WOULD LOVE TO HAVE
THE PLEASURE
OF ESCORTING
YOU SOMETIME!
OH! I'D BE HONORED!
FILTHY SCUM...
SUCKING UP TO THE FEDERATION
TO ADVANCE THEIR OWN
INTERESTS!
Regene:
VERY SOON NOW...
(Thinking)
REGENE REGETTA...
EXCUSE ME.
HUH?
PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME IS RIBBONS ALMARK,
MY DEAR.
WOULD YOU CARE TO DANCE?
THIS IS HIM...
THIS IS LIKE OUR DAY OFF. YOU
SHOULD BE IN THERE HAVING FUN.
THAT SORT OF THING
DOESN'T INTEREST ME.
(Gasping)
Louise:
THAT GUY...
♪
MY, HOW LOVELY.
I NEVER IMAGINED YOU'D
SHOW UP LOOKING LIKE THIS.
IT'S COMMON KNOWLEDGE THAT ALL
THE MEISTERS ARE MEN.
I'M MERELY FOLLOWING OUR
TACTICAL FORECASTER'S ORDERS.
EXCUSE ME.
I KNOW YOU FROM JAPAN.
IT'S LOUISE HALEVY...
SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
Y‐YOU REMEMBER ME?
(Giggling)
THAT'S BECAUSE
IT'S SUCH AN UNCOMMON NAME!
♪
WERE YOU THE ONE WHO SENT
REGENE REGETTA TO SEE ME?
OH NO.
I'M ALSO BEING TOSSED HITHER AND
YON IN HIS LITTLE GAMES.
I HEARD YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S ATTEMPTING TO CARRY OUT
AEOLIA SCHENBERG'S PLAN.
YOU DON'T BELIEVE IT?
IF YOU WISH, I CAN
RETURN THEM TO YOU RIGHT NOW.
YOUR ACCESS RIGHTS
TO VEDA.
(Gasps)
ACCESS RIGHTS?
YOU'RE SAYING YOU ACTUALLY
HAVE CONTROL OF THEM?
(Slight laugh)
(Applause)
WHAT SAY WE GO
SOMEPLACE ELSE...
HMM.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I'M GONNA GO BACK TO WORK.
I'M WORKING AS HARD AS I CAN
TO SPEED UP DEVELOPMENT
OF THE NEW MODEL.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE ANYWAY?
I'M HERE ON BUSINESS.
WHAT KIND OF BUSINESS?
IT HAS TO DO WITH
ORBITAL ELEVATORS.
OH.
SO, IS HE DOING OKAY?
HE?
YOU KNOW. THE GUY WHO USED TO
LIVE RIGHT NEXT DOOR TO YOU.
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT
SAJI CROSSROAD?
YES.
(Gentle sigh)
I RAN INTO HIM BY
COINCIDENCE AT WORK ONE DAY.
OH, REALLY?
YEAH. HE WAS WORKING
UP IN THE COLONIES.
Tieria:
SO YOU'RE SERIOUS WHEN YOU SAY
YOU SEIZED CONTROL OF VEDA.
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE
TO RECALL FOR YOURSELF.
(Gasping)
YOU MEAN... YOU...
Tieria:
THE FORCED DISENGAGEMENT
OF THE TRIAL SYSTEM
I WAS USING ON THE THRONES!
AND THE ONE WHO GAVE...
THE PSEUDO GN DRIVES
TO THE U. N. FORCES.
BUT WHY?
BECAUSE THE PLAN
EXPLICITLY CALLED FOR...
THE DESTRUCTION OF
CELESTIAL BEING.
ACCORDING TO THE PLAN,
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE
ELIMINATED FOUR YEARS AGO.
(Gasping)
YOU'RE KIDDING.
Louise:
I SEE. SO SAJI'S IN SPACE.
THAT MEANS...
HE REALIZED HIS DREAM.
HUH?
YOUR ARM...
OH...
WELL, I HAD
A LITTLE ACCIDENT.
(Gasps)
(Saji's voice)
BECAUSE OF YOU GUYS
THE PERSON I LOVED
WAS INJURED...
Setsuna:
I'M SORRY.
IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
Louise:
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
Tieria:
THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT!
I KNOW THAT AEOLIA SCHENBERG
ENTRUSTED IT ALL TO US.
THE GUNDAMS.
AND THE GN DRIVES.
AND THE TRANS‐AM SYSTEM.
YOU KNOW,
WHEN I MET SAJI
(Gasping)
WHEN I MET HIM,
I FELT THAT HE...
EVEN NOW HE'S STILL...
THINKING OF YOU.
(Gasping in pain)
WHAT'S WRONG?
(Struggling with pain)
WARRANT OFFICER!
HUH?
AS SOMEONE TO WHOM
AEOLIA ENTRUSTED A GUNDAM
I THINK THAT ALL OF YOU
ARE WRONG.
THAT'S RIGHT,
I'LL CONTINUE
DOWN THE PATH I BELIEVE IN!
CALL ME A FOOL IF YOU WANT!
BUT I'LL STICK WITH IT
TO THE END!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE SUDDENLY COLLAPSED IN PAIN.
YOU...
YOU'RE FROM...
CELESTIAL BEING!
(Mocking laughter)
YOU'VE BEEN INFLUENCED BY THE
HUMANS FAR MORE THAN I EXPECTED.
YOU'VE ALLOWED THAT MAN TO
GET DEEP INTO YOUR HEART.
LOCKON STRATOS.
(Angry breath)
HE PLACED VENGEANCE FOR HIS
LOST FAMILY OVER
CARRYING OUT THE PLAN.
SUCH A FOOLISH HUMAN.
(Angry gasp)
BASTARD!
(Gunshot)
(Gasping)
I'M HILING CARE.
I'M AN INNOVATOR, TOO.
(Growling)
(Glass shattering)
I KNOW HIM!
THIS MAN IS A MEMBER OF
CELESTIAL BEING!
GUARDS! GUARDS!
WARRANT OFFICER,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?!
(Louise panting with pain)
(Gulping pills)
(Whimpering)
WARRANT OFFICER...
SO YOU'RE A...
ALTHOUGH AEOLIA SCHENBERG
WORKED OUT HIS PLAN
UP UNTIL
THE THIRD STAGE,
HE WAS OBSESSIVELY ATTACHED
TO THE FIRST STAGE,
THE ELIMINATION OF CONFLICTS.
Regene:
WILL IT BE THE DESIGN
OF RIBBONS ALMARK...
OR THE IDEALS OF
CELESTIAL BEING?
WHICHEVER ONE PREVAILS,
THIS WORLD WILL CHANGE.
♪
I'M SORRY,
I REALLY SCREWED UP.
Tieria:
IT DOESN'T MATTER...
I FOUND IT SETSUNA!
THE TWISTEDNESS
THAT'S IN THE WORLD.
WITH THE GUNDAMS
WE WILL ELIMINATE IT...
THE SOURCE OF THE TWISTEDNESS!
EASIER SAID THAN DONE!
Setsuna:
IT'S THAT GUNDAM!
IT'S AN IMPROVED
THRONE MODEL!
IT'S...
HIM AGAIN!
Al‐Saachez:
ALL RIGHT!
LET'S GET STARTED!
IT'S A WAR...
BETWEEN GUNDAMS OF
EPIC PROPORTIONS!
Narrator:
TIED DOWN BY MEMORIES,
AND WITH AN UNCERTAIN
FUTURE ON THE HORIZON,
WHAT ARE PEOPLE
THINKING?
NEXT EPISODE:
"THE INDELIBLE PAST".
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
EVEN TOMORROW
HAS BECOME
JUST ANOTHER MEMORY.