Spokesperson #26A:
THERE IS NO DOUBT IT WAS
GUNDAMS THAT ATTACKED
THE DETENTION CENTER FOR
ANTI‐GOVERNMENT ELEMENTS.
ARE THEY STILL AFFILIATED WITH
CELESTIAL BEING?
WHAT ABOUT THE RUMOR THESE
PARTICULAR GUNDAMS
WERE ACTUALLY DEVELOPED
BY A DISSIDENT GROUP?
WHILE THOSE ARE STILL
UNSUBSTANTIATED RUMORS,
EITHER WAY IT'S CLEAR THEY ARE
ENGAGING IN TERRORIST ACTS
THAT THREATEN OUR
PRESENT POLITICAL SYSTEM.
IN ORDER TO EXTERMINATE THESE
TERRORISTS...
THE GOVERNMENT
IS DISPATCHING
ITS AUTONOMOUS
PEACEKEEPING FORCE.
(TV running in background)
Regene:
PREDICTING THE REVIVAL OF
CELESTIAL BEING,
AND USING IT TO
EXPAND THE POWER OF A‐LAWS...
WAS THIS SOMETHING
YOU THOUGHT UP?
OR WAS IT
VEDA'S IDEA?
AH, YES... WHOSE WAS IT?
Revive:
IN ANY CASE...IT'S ABOUT TIME
FOR US TO MAKE OUR OWN MOVES.
REVIVE REVIVAL.
I THOUGHT YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT
THE GADESSA'S BEEN ROLLED OUT.
IT'S READY TO
SORTIE RIGHT NOW...
JUST SAY THE WORD.
THANK YOU BUT THAT
WON'T BE NECESSARY, REVIVE.
I'VE ASKED SOMEONE ELSE
TO TAKE CARE OF THIS
PARTICULAR
OPERATION.
SOMEONE ELSE?
DO YOU MEAN DIVINE?
OR DID YOU CALL IN BRING?
ACTUALLY, HE'S HUMAN.
THOUGH IN A WAY...
HE SEEMS TO HAVE
TRANSCENDED THOSE LIMITATIONS
♪
(Mileina yawning)
STAYING HERE
TO WATCH THE SHIP IS BORING!
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WE'RE OVERSEEING REPAIRS TO
PTOLEMAIOS,
ANALYZING THE NEW
A‐LAWS MOBILE SUIT,
TUNING 00'S TWIN
DRIVE SYSTEM...
THERE IS MORE THAN ENOUGH
TO DO RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, BUT NONE OF
THAT STUFF IS ANY FUN!
Tieria:
A PLACE LIKE THIS...
I'M SURPRISED THE FEDERATION
HASN'T FOUND IT BY NOW.
THE FEDERATION SCATTERS GN
PARTICLES IN THE MIDDLE EAST
WHICH HAS
A LOT OF NON‐MEMBER NATIONS.
OFFICIALLY, IT'S USING THE
PARTICLE EFFECTS
TO DISRUPT THE COMMUNICATIONS
OF TERROR NETWORKS.
BUT ITS REAL GOAL
IS TO PARALYZE
THE ECONOMIC GROWTH
OF MIDDLE EASTERN COUNTRIES.
SIMPLY PUT, DO WHAT THE
FEDERATION SAYS
OR YOU'RE IN FOR
A ROUGH TIME.
BUT, ON THE OTHER HAND, THANKS
TO THE GN PARTICLES,
THE KATHARON BASE HASN'T
BEEN DISCOVERED YET.
YOU SURE
KNOW A LOT.
OH, YOU THINK SO?
WELL, IT'S JUST
COMMON SENSE REALLY...
Announcer:
ARE YOU READING ME?
WE'VE CONFIRMED YOUR MOBILE
SUITS. WE'RE OPENING THE HATCH.
Setsuna:
ROGER.
(Impressed murmuring)
SO THESE
ARE GUNDAMS!
YEAH! THE HEROIC MACHINES
THAT SAVED AZADISTAN!
IT'S A REAL HONOR TO HAVE YOU
WITH US, CELESTIAL BEING!
YEAH, WELCOME!
WON'T YOU
SHOW US YOUR FACES?
OH, RIGHT.
MY FAULT.
Tieria:
OUR IDENTITIES
ARE SECRET!
DON'T BE SUCH
A STICKLER FOR RULES.
THEY HELPED US OUT,
DIDN'T THEY?
(Scoffs)
(Thinking)
THE ANTI‐GOVERNMENT
ORGANIZATION... KATHARON...
WE'RE GRATEFUL YOU AGREED TO
MEET WITH US.
I'M KLAUS GRAD OF THE KATHARON
MIDDLE EASTERN BRANCH.
WE REPRESENT
CELESTIAL BEING.
THAT'S ALL
WE CAN SAY.
THAT'S FINE, WE UNDERSTAND
YOUR SITUATION.
I'M VERY GRATEFUL
YOU RESCUED PRINCESS MARINA
FROM THAT CENTER.
FROM NOW ON WE'LL ASSUME
RESPONSIBILITY FOR HER SAFETY.
SHIRIN...
WOULD YOU RATHER WE LEFT YOU
WITH CELESTIAL BEING?
BUT WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH A
GROUP OF DISSIDENTS?
SOMETHING WRONG
WITH THAT?
(Sighs)
THERE'S SOMEONE ELSE WE'D LIKE
TO LEAVE WITH YOU.
THIS IS SAJI CROSSROAD.
HE'S A CIVILIAN.
HE WAS ACCUSED OF BEING
A MEMBER OF KATHARON
EVEN THOUGH HE'S
COMPLETELY INNOCENT.
WELL, I'M REALLY SORRY
TO HEAR ABOUT THAT.
YOU CAN REST ASSURED THAT WE'LL
TAKE GOOD CARE OF HIM, TOO.
HOLD ON,
DON'T I HAVE A SAY?
IT'S THE BEST OPTION
FOR ALL OF US.
(Laughing)
HEY, WHATCHA DOING?
HOLD ON, YOU CAN'T JUST
BARGE IN HERE LIKE THAT.
THEY HAVE KIDS HERE...
(Gasps)
DON'T TELL ME...
ARE YOU ACTUALLY
RAISING THESE CHILDREN
TO BE MEMBERS OF
KATHARON?
HMM?
DON'T MISUNDERSTAND US.
ALL WE'RE DOING HERE IS TAKING
CARE OF CHILDREN
WHO'VE BEEN ORPHANED.
THE FEDERATION'S
ONE‐SIDED POLICIES
HERE IN THE MIDDLE EAST...
CAUSE REAL DAMAGE.
AND THEY ARE
THE LIVING PROOF.
THOUGH BECAUSE WE HAVE LIMITED
ACCESS TO FUNDS...
WE CAN'T TAKE
IN EVERY CHILD WE'D LIKE TO.
(Gasps)
PRINCESS MARINA!
YOU ARE PRINCESS
MARINA ISMAIL, RIGHT?
YES, I AM.
HEY, I KNOW
WHO SHE IS, TOO!
WOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M REALLY
TALKING TO THE PRINCESS!
PRINCESS MARINA...
WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
IF YOU SPENT SOME TIME
WITH THE CHILDREN?
OF COURSE.
WOW, REALLY?
THIS WAY, THIS WAY!
ME, TOO! ME, TOO!
(Children giggling)
HMM.
WELL, SHE'S NOT A LIVING SYMBOL
OF OUR NATION FOR NOTHING.
NOW, I'D LIKE TO GET TO
THE MAIN ISSUE AT HAND...
IN ORDER FOR OUR GROUP,
KATHARON,
TO OVERTHROW THE CURRENT
FEDERATION GOVERNMENT‐‐
LOOK, I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT,
UNLIKE YOUR GROUP,
OUR ACTIONS
AREN'T BASED ON ANY
KIND OF POLITICAL IDEOLOGY.
BUT I THOUGHT YOU WERE TAKING A
POSITION AGAINST THE FEDERATION.
THAT'S NOT SO, OUR ENEMY IS NOT
THE FEDERATION GOVERNMENT,
BUT
THE A‐LAWS.
Shirin:
THAT'S WHAT YOU SAY, BUT DOESN'T
YOUR GOAL OF FIGHTING
THE GOVERNMENT'S
AUTONOMOUS FORCE
DIRECTLY COINCIDE
WITH OUR GOALS?
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
IN ORDER TO HALT THE EVIL DEEDS
OF THE A‐LAWS,
BOTH OUR GROUPS
SHOULD JOIN FORCES!
UNFORTUNATELY,
THE MOBILE SUITS YOU HAVE HERE
CAN'T COMPETE AGAINST THOSE
EQUIPPED WITH GN DRIVES.
BUT EVEN SO...
WE'RE QUITE SERIOUS ABOUT
COOPERATING WITH YOU.
EVEN SUPPLIES,
MAINTENANCE...
WE WANT TO
HELP YOUR CAUSE.
LOSING THE TRILOBITE LIKE THAT
WAS QUITE THE BLUNDER, MAJOR.
I AM ASHAMED
OF MY FAILURE, SIR.
COLONEL MANNEQUIN. YOU AND THE
MAJOR WILL SHARE COMMAND.
SIR.
REMEMBER THAT WE A‐LAWS HAVE TO
BE THE SHIELD
AND SPEAR OF THE
FEDERATION ITSELF.
FAILURE IS UNFORGIVABLE.
(Frustrated grunt)
SO, THERE YOU HAVE IT.
FROM THIS POINT ON YOU'LL BE
FOLLOWING MY ORDERS AS WELL.
IS THAT UNDERSTOOD,
MR. BUSHIDO?
I CATEGORICALLY
REFUSE.
WHAT?
HEADQUARTERS HAS GIVEN ME
PERMISSION TO ACT AS I SEE FIT.
THINK OF ME
AS A ONE‐MAN ARMY.
AN ARMED FORCE MADE UP OF A
SINGLE SOLDIER.
SUCH SELFISHNESS‐‐
I TOLD YOU I HAVE PERMISSION.
OH, SO YOU'VE BEEN MOBILIZED,
COLONEL?
I'VE BEEN ENTRUSTED WITH A FORCE
THAT'S LOOKING FOR GUNDAMS.
TO THINK THE REGULAR FORCES ARE
NOW SERVING
AS SOME KIND OF
ERRAND BOY FOR THE A‐LAWS.
IS THAT SO?
BY THE WAY,
HOW'S HE HOLDING UP OUT THERE?
UHH...
YOU MEAN LIEUTENANT ANDREI?
HE'S ALWAYS VERY DEVOTED
TO HIS DUTIES.
Sergei:
I GUESS HE'S
SENDING ME A MESSAGE.
AS YOU CAN PROBABLY TELL,
HE HATES ME.
SIR?
I WAS A DILIGENT SOLDIER,
BUT I WAS NEVER REALLY WHAT
YOU'D CALL A GOOD PARENT TO HIM.
COLONEL I...
(Sighs)
COLONEL,
I'M THINKING OF TAKING YOU UP ON
THAT OFFER WE DISCUSSED.
OFFER?
WHEN WE TALKED ABOUT YOU
ADOPTING ME AS YOUR DAUGHTER.
DO YOU REALLY MEAN THAT?
WE CAN GO OVER THE DETAILS
NEXT TIME WE MEET.
LATER.
I AM A FORTUNATE GIRL.
PRINCESS MARINA!
LOOK AT THESE, TOO!
YES, WELL,
BEFORE WE GET STARTED...
DID YOU WANT
TO COME OVER HERE TOO?
HMM.
HUH?
THERE.
COME AND PLAY WITH US,
LITTLE ONE.
UH...
(Hesitating)
(Whimpers)
(Gunshot)
(Tense grunt)
(Sighs)
THOSE CHILDREN ARE YOUR
VICTIMS TOO, YOU KNOW.
VICTIMS OF THE WORLD
THAT YOU GUYS CHANGED.
IT'S TRUE.
I KNOW IT.
DOESN'T THAT MAKE YOU
FEEL ANYTHING?
SURE, I FEEL SOMETHING.
THAT'S WHY I'D NEVER
BE ABLE TO JOIN
THEM AND PLAY LIKE THAT.
SO, IF YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING
THEN WHY DO YOU KEEP
FIGHTING?
I HAVE MY REASONS.
I DOUBT
YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
HATE ME IF YOU WANT.
SETSUNA...
(Growling)
SETSUNA, WAIT.
(Panting)
ARE YOU LEAVING?
THAT'S RIGHT...
BEFORE YOU GO,
I HAVE ONE LAST
IMPORTANT REQUEST
TO ASK OF YOU.
HUH?
WELL, IT LOOKS AS THOUGH
THERE'S NO CHANCE
CELESTIAL BEING IS
GOING TO JOIN US.
I GUESS NOT.
BUT THEIR RESPONSE
WAS ENOUGH.
THE FIGHT AGAINST A‐LAWS IS
GOING TO BE EXTREMELY BRUTAL.
THAT MEANS SOMETIME
IN THE FUTURE,
WE WILL BE JOINING
HANDS AND WORKING TOGETHER.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
JEAN ONE?
I GUESS...
HARD TO SAY, REALLY...
HEY, HOW LONG ARE YOU
GUYS GOING TO KEEP GOOFING OFF?
GET BACK TO YOUR STATIONS AND
START WORKING!
Allelujah:
IS OUR MEETING OVER?
Setsuna:
YEAH. BUT THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
I HAVE TO DO.
Tieria:
SOMETHING ELSE?
I'LL BE ESCORTING
MARINA ISMAIL
BACK TO THE COUNTRY OF
AZADISTAN.
SO, YOU'RE SAYING...
ARE YOU SURE
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT?
I'M TRULY SORRY FOR ALL
THE TROUBLE I'M CAUSING.
HMM...
WELL, YOU CAN'T GO BACK
IN A GUNDAM.
ON THE OFF CHANCE
YOU'RE DISCOVERED...
YOU COULD BRING FURTHER HARM
DOWN UPON AZADISTAN.
THEN LET ME HAVE
THE USE OF THIS CRAFT.
YOU CAN USE
THE GUNDAM.
THAT'LL WORK.
AND DON'T FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE
TO COME BACK, EITHER.
THAT'S ABSURD.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU
OVER THESE PAST FOUR YEARS?
FOR YOU TO ACTUALLY
TELL A JOKE IS...
I WAS SERIOUS
BACK THERE.
WHAT?
(Chuckles)
NOW, THAT WAS A JOKE.
CELESTIAL BEING AND
KATHARON...
BOTH OF THEM ARE
GROUPS THAT CAUSE FIGHTING!
I CAN'T STAY
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS!
HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING THERE?
NOTHING!
I WAS JUST...
OH, YOU'RE WITH CELESTIAL BEING,
AREN'T YOU?
HUH?
I'VE GOT COMRADES
IN TOWN I NEED TO TALK TO.
NEAREST TOWN IS A LONG WAY FROM
HERE, TAKE A VEHICLE!
HUH?
THANK YOU!
HAVE YOU SEEN PRINCESS MARINA
WANDERING AROUND?
I JUST SAW HER WITH SOME
CELESTIAL BEING PEOPLE
A FEW
MOMENTS AGO.
SHE WAS WITH THEM?
Announcer:
THE GUNDAMS ARE RETURNING TO
THEIR MOTHER SHIP!
OPEN THE HATCH!
(Gasps)
COULD...
COULD SHE BE...?
WE HAVE TO
STOP THEM FROM TAKING OFF!
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE NOW.
MARINA...
♪
I WONDER IF I CAN MAKE IT ACROSS
THE WHOLE DESERT IN THIS.
HUH?
(Stammering)
THE FEDERATION!
WHY ARE YOU CROSSING THE DESERT
WITH SO LITTLE EQUIPMENT?
(Panting)
WE GOT A HIT
ON HIS BIOMETRICS.
OUR FRIEND HERE IS A
MEMBER OF KATHARON!
I'M NOT!
I SWEAR I'VE NEVER BEEN
A MEMBER OF THAT GROUP!
ENOUGH
OF YOUR LYING!
STOP, THERE'S NO NEED
TO ROUGH HIM UP!
WHA‐‐
COLONEL!
Sergei:
GET OUT.
I WANT TO HEAR
HIS STORY.
(Growling)
YOU'RE NOT REALLY A SOLDIER,
ARE YOU, BOY?
HMM?
I'M AN OLD SOLDIER,
I CAN TELL THESE THINGS.
YOU DON'T HAVE THE EYES OF
SOMEONE WHO'S SEEN COMBAT.
IN OTHER WORDS, YOU'RE CLEARLY
NOT A MEMBER OF KATHARON.
SO, WHAT IN THE WORLD
HAVE YOU BEEN UP TO?
HUH.
YOU'VE BEEN TRAVELING WITH
CELESTIAL BEING, HAVEN'T YOU?
(Gasps)
IT'S PLAUSIBLE.
ACCORDING TO THE DATA,
UNTIL A FEW WEEKS AGO,
YOU WERE WORKING ON
COLONY DEVELOPMENT AT PROUD,
WHERE THE GUNDAMS FIRST
RE‐APPEARED.
AND NOW YOU'RE IN THE SAME
REGION WHERE THERE WAS
A BATTLE YESTERDAY
WITH THE GUNDAMS.
IT'S NOTHING.
IT'S JUST
SIMPLE REASONING.
I'M...
...NOT WITH KATHARON OR
CELESTIAL BEING.
I BELIEVE YOU.
I JUST WANT TO HEAR
YOUR SIDE OF THE STORY, BOY.
I WON'T
USE IT AGAINST YOU.
(Gasps)
Saji:
CAN YOU GET ME
CLEARED OF ALL SUSPICIONS?
Sergei:
I'LL DO WHAT I CAN.
Zinin:
CAPTAIN BARACK ZININ, SIR.
WITH ALL FIVE MEMBERS
OF SPACE TEAM FOUR.
PRESENT
AND REPORTING FOR DUTY.
GOOD WORK, TEAM.
Goodman:
WHAT?
IS THIS TRUE?
I'LL ISSUE THE ORDERS
IMMEDIATELY.
IF WE LEFT IT
TO THAT NAÏVE WOMAN,
SHE'D BE SURE TO
MESS THIS UP.
EXCELLENT NEWS,
COMMANDER.
WE'VE DISCOVERED
KATHARON'S MILITARY BASE,
AND THERE'S A VERY GOOD CHANCE
THE GUNDAMS ARE THERE TOO.
WE NEED TO ATTEND
TO THIS IMMEDIATELY.
SIR!
COMMANDER, PERMISSION FOR OUR
TEAM TO SORTIE AS WELL.
NO NEED
TO PUSH YOURSELVES.
TAKE IT EASY
FOR NOW.
(Frustrated sigh)
THE GUNDAMS ARE OUT THERE,
AND YET...
Kati:
WH... WHAT KIND
OF AN ORDER IS THIS?
WE'RE EXPECTED TO MAKE USE OF
AUTOMATONS IN KILL MODE?
THIS IS CRAZY!
THIS OPERATION IS BARBARIC!
COLONEL.
AN ORDER FROM THAT HIGH UP HAS
TO BE STRICTLY FOLLOWED.
YOU'RE TELLING ME YOU DON'T
THINK THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
ABOUT THE DETAILS
OF THIS OPERATION?
NOW WHY WOULD I
THINK SUCH A THING?
WE'RE FIGHTING THE
ANTI‐GOVERNMENT FORCES.
THERE'S NO NEED TO SHOW THEM
ANY MERCY, NOW IS THERE?
(Frustrated sigh)
AN OPERATION
LIKE THIS ONE...
NOW, I FINALLY UNDERSTAND
WHY THE COLONEL
WAS SO FIRMLY
OPPOSED TO MY REASSIGNMENT.
YOU'VE GOT HIM WRONG,
LIEUTENANT.
COLONEL SMIRNOV
IS THE KIND OF MAN
WHO WOULD ABANDON HIS OWN
FLESH AND BLOOD
TO MAKE SURE HE
FULFILLED HIS DUTY.
HIS FLESH AND BLOOD?
YES, THAT MAN ALLOWED
MY MOTHER TO DIE.
(Gasps)
(Uneasy sigh)
Liu Mei:
SO...
THE A‐LAWS KNOW
WHERE THE DISSIDENTS ARE.
I UNDERSTAND.
I'LL LET TIERIA
AND THE OTHERS KNOW.
Sergei:
YOU IDIOT!
(Slam)
WHO TOLD YOU TO
REPORT THIS INFO TO A‐LAWS?
BUT SIR, IT'S OUR DUTY
TO REPORT THESE THINGS!
THAT IS MY DECISION TO MAKE,
SOLDIER!
HUH?
MR. CROSSROAD.
COME WITH ME, YOU HAVE TO GET
OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I'M AFRAID YOUR PRESENCE HERE
WAS LEAKED TO THE A‐LAWS.
THEY'RE A GROUP THAT OPERATES
ABOVE THE LAW.
I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH AUTHORITY TO
PROTECT YOU WHEN THEY SHOW UP.
BUT THAT'S‐‐
YOU HAVE TO HURRY!
SOMEBODY LEAKED THE FACT
THAT I WAS THERE...
SO, DOES THAT MEAN THAT‐‐
HUH?
THAT COLOR!
Feldt:
EMERGENCY CODED MESSAGE
FROM WANG LIU MEI.
APPARENTLY AN A‐LAWS
MOBILE SUIT TEAM
IS HEADED DIRECTLY
FOR THE KATHARON BASE.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO NOW?
WE'RE GOING
TO GO HELP THEM.
ANTI‐SATELLITE
OPTICAL CAMOUFLAGE,
EMERGENCY ASCENT!
TELL THE GUNDAMS
TO GET READY TO LAUNCH.
THAT'S A ROGER!
Feldt:
PTOLEMY BEGINNING
EMERGENCY ASCENT.
0043 UNTIL SURFACING.
THE A‐LAWS
FOUND THEIR BASE...?
BUT THERE ARE A LOT OF INNOCENT
CHILDREN WITH THEM, AS WELL.
HURRY IT UP!
DAMN IT, WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF
TIME, HURRY IT UP!
(Siren wails)
IT'S AN A‐LAWS
MOBILE SUIT TEAM!
WAIT, ARE THEY GOING TO
ATTACK THIS PLACE?
HOW MANY OF THEM
ARE COMING?
BUT HOW DID THEY
FIND OUT ABOUT OUR BASE?
IT COULDN'T HAVE BEEN FROM
CELESTIAL BEING, COULD IT?
QUICKLY, GET THE CHILDREN
TO THE SHELTER!
O‐OKAY!
KLAUS, LET'S GO OUT
AND FIGHT!
NO, WE'RE STILL
TOO BADLY OUTMATCHED!
WE'LL STRENGTHEN
OUR DEFENSES
AND WAIT FOR CELESTIAL BEING
TO COME TO OUR AID!
ARE THEY EVEN
GOING TO SHOW UP?
I BELIEVE IN THEM!
(Startled yelling)
THEY'RE BOMBING US?
(Panicked murmuring)
(People screaming)
Andrei:
I HAVE VISUAL CONFIRMATION
OF A STRUCTURE THAT
LOOKS LIKE AN ENEMY BASE.
HUH?
(Rapid blasting)
Andrei:
ENEMY MOBILE SUITS!
THEY'RE STILL USING OUTDATED
MOBILE SUITS.
(Frustrated sigh)
Commander #3:
COMMENCE MOPPING‐UP
OPERATION OF ENEMY BASE.
RELEASE AUTOMATONS.
Pilot #30A:
ROGER.
THEY WOULDN'T...
Pilot #30A:
RELEASING AUTOMATONS.
NO, WAIT A MINUTE!
(Coughing)
WAIT...
THOSE ARE...
(Mechanical marching)
THEY'RE MILITARY
AUTOMATONS!
EVERYONE,
FALL BACK, NOW!
FALL BACK!
(Blast)
DAMN, WE'RE TOO LATE!
WHAT ABOUT
THE KATHARON PEOPLE?
Lyle:
I'LL LEAVE THIS
TO YOU GUYS!
GET A MOVE ON,
GUNDAM!
Commander #3:
PERIES! INTERCEPT
THAT FIRST GUNDAM!
Peries:
ROGER!
(Blasting rapidly)
HE'S GOT
SOME MOVES!
Commander #3:
ALL MACHINES
AFTER THE OTHER GUNDAMS!
Bushido:
I'LL BE SITTING
THIS ONE OUT.
Commander #3:
MR. BUSHIDO?
BUT WHY?
I DON'T FEEL LIKE IT!
(Gasping)
THIS IS...
IS THIS...
IS THIS SOMETHING
HUMAN BEINGS WOULD DO?
(Gasping)
Allelujah:
MASS MURDER
WITH AUTOMATED WEAPONS.
(Pilot screaming)
YOU THINK JUST BECAUSE YOU AVOID
PULLING THE TRIGGER YOURSELF
YOU WON'T FEEL ANY OF THE
GUILT FROM COMMITTING THE CRIME?
READY DOUBLE BAZOOKA...
BURST MODE!
Commander #3:
WE'VE ACHIEVED OUR
INITIAL OBJECTIVE!
TIME TO WITHDRAW!
(Rapid machine‐gun fire)
(Gasps)
(Tense sigh)
Lyle:
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU!
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU
FOR THIS, A‐LAWS!
DON'T YOU DARE RUN!
DON'T YOU DARE
RUN AWAY FROM ME, A‐LAWS!
Feldt:
IT'S HORRIBLE...
(Trembling sigh)
Allelujah:
SO THIS IS...
A‐LAWS...
Tieria:
THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS IS THE ENEMY
WE ARE SWORN TO DEFEAT!
(Sighing)
I'M A SUPER‐SOLDIER.
I ONLY EXIST
TO FIGHT.
AND YET I TRIED TO FIND
THE HAPPINESS
THAT NORMAL PEOPLE
TAKE FOR GRANTED.
COLONEL, COULD THIS BE
MY PUNISHMENT...
FOR WANTING THAT?
(Grieving sighs)
ALL BECAUSE...
ALL THIS BECAUSE
I TALKED TO THEM...
(Sobbing)
THIS CAN'T BE...
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
♪
Setsuna:
WE'LL BE IN AZADISTAN
SHORTLY.
I'M RETURNING
AFTER ALL.
THAT'S RIGHT.
BACK TO YOUR COUNTRY.
HMM.
(Gasping)
AZADISTAN IS...
EVERYTHING'S BURNING...
Marina:
BUT WHY IS AZADISTAN...
WHY?
THE SCALE...
NOT TERRORISTS.
(Gasping)
IT'S...
A GUNDAM!
AND THAT COLOR!
IS IT HIM?
Al‐Saachez:
THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU GUESSED RIGHT, PUNK!
Narrator:
A LOST PAST,
A LOST NORMAL LIFE,
A LOST NATION...
EACH ONE OF THESE IS
TEARING APART SOMEONE'S HEART.
NEXT EPISODE:
"SCARS".
THE ACHE FROM THE
DULL PAIN CALLED REGRET.