Feldt:
TWO MACHINES ARE CLOSING IN
ON THE SHIP!
THOSE TWO BROKE THROUGH!
Ian:
FIRE! SHOOT AT THEM!
(Nervous grunt)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
FIRE!
Saji, in memory:
KILLING SOMEONE WOULD MAKE ME
THE SAME AS YOU GUYS.
Ian:
WHAT'S WRONG? HURRY UP!
BUT IF YOU FIGHT,
MORE INNOCENT PEOPLE
WILL BE HURT!
(Tense gasping)
Saji:
NO, DON'T!
Tieria:
THOSE CHILDREN ARE
YOUR VICTIMS TOO, YOU KNOW.
STAY BACK!
CELESTIAL BEING!
(Gasps)
STAY BACK!
(Grunts)
Andrei:
WE'RE TOO FAR IN FRONT!
PULL BACK,
WARRANT OFFICER!
BUT I WAS‐‐
THAT'S AN ORDER!
(Frustrated growl)
(Shaky breathing)
SO, YOU COULDN'T FIRE BACK.
WELL, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
♪
Graham:
IS THIS ALL YOU'VE GOT?!
(Frustrated grunt)
TAKING IT EASY ON ME?
OR IS THIS AN ATTEMPT
TO INSULT ME?!
(Thinking)
AT THIS RATE, WE'LL...
Allelujah:
PLEASE, MARIE, STOP IT!
IT'S ME,
ALLELUJAH!
I AM A SUPER SOLDIER!
Graham:
GUNDAM!
THIS IS YOUR REQUIEM!
Peries:
(Aggressive yell)
(Cries in pain)
(Gasps)
MARIE!
Graham:
HUH?
(Yells)
Graham:
LOOK AT THAT!
THAT'S RIGHT,
THIS IS WHAT
I WANTED TO FIGHT!
(Aggressive cry)
(Gasps)
SIMPLY INCREDIBLE!
Allelujah:
MARIE!
(Crash)
HUH?
WHAT THE...
I'M NEVER LETTING YOU GO
AGAIN, MARIE!
THIS GUY IS...
Setsuna:
GOTCHA!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
IT'S AN OVERLOAD!
I SEE.
HE'S HAVING PROBLEMS
WITH HIS SUIT!
(Startled gasp)
DEFEATING YOU LIKE THIS
IS WORTHLESS!
Zinin:
MR. BUSHIDO!
ALL MACHINES, SURROUND
THE DOUBLE POWERED ONE!
ROGER!
Tieria:
SETSUNA!
(Grunts)
Tieria:
SETSUNA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
Setsuna:
IT'S THE TWIN DRIVE.
Sumeragi:
ALL GUNDAMS, FALL BACK.
SUMERAGI LEE NORIEGA?
WE HAVE TO DIVIDE
THE ENEMY FORCES.
FIRE HIGH DENSITY PARTICLE
AND SMOKE TORPEDOES!
OLD MAN!
I'M ON IT!
CAPTAIN! IT'S SMOKE!
OUR VISUAL SIGNALS WILL BE LOST!
Operator:
SMOKE IN THE COMBAT AIRSPACE,
MA'AM.
MOBILE SUIT COMMUNICATIONS
ARE BEING DISRUPTED
DUE TO
INCREASED PARTICLE DENSITY!
CHANGING TACTICS AT
THIS STAGE?
WE'RE GOING TO REGROUP!
SIGNAL A WITHDRAWAL!
ROGER!
Lockon:
THEY'RE RETREATING?
Tieria:
LOOKS LIKE IT.
ARIOS ISN'T THERE!
I CAN'T LOCATE IT!
Feldt:
ALLELUJAH'S...
WHAT'D SHE SAY?!
Sumeragi:
THERE'S NO RESPONSE FROM ARIOS?!
Feldt:
MISS SUMERAGI!
Lasse:
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
WE HAVE TO FIND OUT
ARIOS' LAST POINT OF COMBAT
FROM THE MISSION RECORDER.
Sumeragi:
AFTER RETRIEVING 00,
SEND SERAVEE AND CHERUDIM
TO LOOK FOR ARIOS.
R‐ROGER THAT.
Zinin:
MR. BUSHIDO!
NO MATTER WHO YOU ARE,
THAT WAS UNACCEPTABLE!
Graham:
I'M NOT LISTENING TO YOU.
Louise:
LIEUTENANT PERIES' AHEAD
ISN'T HERE.
THAT MEANS...
LIEUTENANT.
Kati:
FORM A SEARCH PARTY IMMEDIATELY!
HOW AM I GOING TO TELL
COLONEL SMIRNOV?
Shirin:
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
ANYONE'S FOLLOWING US.
I'D SAY CELESTIAL BEING
MANAGED TO DRAW THE A‐LAWS
FAR ENOUGH AWAY.
SETSUNA.
(Moaning)
HUH?
WHERE'S MARIE?
(Gasps)
MARIE!
(Groaning)
(Gasps)
(Attack grunt)
ST‐STOP IT, MARIE!
PLEASE!
EVEN WITHOUT
MY MOBILE SUIT, I'LL‐‐
(Allelujah and Peries grunt)
A FOOL LIKE YOU
WILL NEVER DEFEAT ME!
(Gasps in pain)
MARIE.
(Grunts in pain)
(Screams)
MARIE!
MARIE PARFACY!
(Startled gasp)
Young Allelujah:
MARIE.
MARIE!
(Shouting)
(Gasps)
(Cries in pain)
MARIE!
(Screams)
ALLELUJAH.
MARIE.
YOU REMEMBER ME.
ALLELUJAH.
HUH?
MARIE!
MARIE PARFACY!
Subordinate:
COLONEL!
THERE'S NO NEED FOR YOU
TO SORTIE PERSONALLY!
YOU'D BETTER STEP BACK!
LIEUTENANT.
Andrei:
ACCORDING TO THE RECORDER DATA,
SHE SHOULD BE IN THIS AREA.
(Frustrated sigh)
LIEUTENANT.
YOU'RE PUSHING YOURSELF
TOO HARD.
WHAT?
I CAN SENSE IT WITH
MY QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES.
IN YOUR HEART, YOU'RE CRYING.
AND NOW THE LIEUTENANT TOO.
IT'S ALWAYS
THE FAULT OF THE GUNDAMS.
HUH?
IT'S THE ORDER TO WITHDRAW!
Kati:
YOU CANCELLED THE LIEUTENANT'S
SEARCH MISSION?!
THAT'S WHAT THE TOP BRASS WANT.
THEY SAY OUR FORCE
MUST TURN ITS ATTENTION
SOLELY TOWARDS
CELESTIAL BEING.
WE'LL LET THE REGULAR FORCES
LOOK FOR THE LIEUTENANT.
(Growls)
Feldt:
CHERUDIM HAS LAUNCHED.
Mileina:
SERAVEE HAS JUST ARRIVED
ON THE CATAPULT DECK.
Sumeragi:
TIERIA, I'VE SENT YOU THE DATA
ON THE AIRSPACE
WHERE ARIOS WAS FIGHTING.
TRY TO AVOID COMBAT
WITH THE A‐LAWS.
STAY FOCUSED ON THE SEARCH.
ROGER.
TIERIA ERDE, HEADING OUT.
Mileina:
SERAVEE HAS LAUNCHED!
BEGINNING PREPARATIONS
TO SUBMERGE!
Ian:
SETSUNA!
DAMN IT, I TOLD YOU
NOT TO USE TRANS‐AM!
LUCKILY FOR US THE TWIN DRIVE
IS STILL WORKING,
BUT EVEN SO...
PLEASE, GET IT REPAIRED.
ALLELUJAH'S...
YEAH.
HEY, OVER HERE!
RIGHT.
SAJI CROSSROAD.
YOU SURE?
YOU HATE GUNDAMS.
UNTIL THE KATHARON PEOPLE
GET AWAY SAFELY,
I'M GONNA DO
ANYTHING I CAN TO HELP.
IT'S RAINING.
Young Peries:
ALLELUJAH?
ALLELUJAH!
(Desperately)
(Gasps)
(Panting)
WHERE AM I?
MARIE.
HEY, THERE.
I SEE YOU'RE AWAKE.
YES,
ALLELUJAH.
I CHECKED OUR MACHINES
PRETTY THOROUGHLY,
BUT ALL THE SYSTEMS
ARE DOWN IN BOTH.
WE WON'T BE ABLE TO
FIX THEM BY OURSELVES.
OH.
LET'S HOPE THAT
SOMEBODY COMES FOR US.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
HMM?
HOW DID YOU EVER END UP
BECOMING THIS SOMA PERIES?
THEY PROBABLY...
IMPLANTED
ANOTHER PERSONALITY,
IN ORDER TO RESTORE
THE FIVE SENSES
THAT I'D LOST.
THEN THE SUPERHUMAN INSTITUTE
MUST HAVE SENT ME
TO THE MILITARY TO SERVE
AS A SUPER SOLDIER
TO MAKE SURE
THEY WOULDN'T BE CLOSED DOWN.
HOW TERRIBLE FOR YOU.
YES.
HMM?
BUT BECAUSE OF ALL THAT,
I COULD FINALLY SEE
WHAT YOU LOOKED LIKE
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
AND I KNEW IT WAS YOU
RIGHT AWAY.
I THINK IT WAS
THE QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES.
YEAH, WELL, HERE I AM
ACTUALLY TALKING TO YOU
FACE TO FACE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT MYSELF.
HEY, NOW CAN I ASK YOU
SOMETHING?
WHAT DID YOU DO
AFTER YOU GOT AWAY
FROM THE LAB?
Allelujah:
WE WERE TRYING TO
AVOID DISPOSAL,
SO MY FRIENDS AND I ESCAPED
THE INSTITUTE TOGETHER.
(Panting)
(Sobs)
AT FIRST, I REGRETTED
NOT TAKING YOU WITH US.
BUT IT WAS A VERY GOOD THING
THAT I DIDN'T.
TELL ME, WHAT HAPPENED?
MY FRIENDS AND I WERE ABLE TO
STEAL A TRANSPORT SHIP
AND ESCAPE THE COLONY.
BUT WE HAD NO PLACE TO GO.
WE JUST KEPT DRIFTING IN SPACE,
UNTIL EVENTUALLY
WE RAN OUT OF FOOD AND AIR.
AND THEN...
NO! I DON'T WANNA DIE!
ALLELUJAH! ALLELUJAH!
IT'S NO GOOD!
YOU'RE GONNA DIE!
ALLELUJAH,
PLEASE.
NO.
MY NAME IS...
Peries:
I KNEW.
I KNEW THAT ANOTHER PERSONALITY
EXISTED INSIDE YOU.
IT DOESN'T EXCUSE
WHAT I DID.
HALLELUJAH IS ME.
BUT‐‐
AS THE SHIP'S SOLE SURVIVOR,
I CURSED MY FATE.
AND THE SUPERHUMAN INSTITUTE,
AND THIS WORLD TOO.
THAT'S WHY,
TO CHANGE THIS WORLD,
I ACCEPTED THE OFFER
TO BE A GUNDAM MEISTER.
BECAUSE THE ONLY THING
SUPER SOLDIERS KNOW
IS HOW TO FIGHT.
MARIE, DO YOU STILL HAVE
THE MEMORIES OF SOMA PERIES?
I HAVE THEM.
AND HER PERSONALITY.
THEN YOU KNOW ABOUT
THE THINGS THAT I'VE DONE.
I...
I KILLED THEM ALL.
AT MY HANDS.
OUR FRIENDS,
AND OUR SIBLINGS.
I TOOK THEIR LIVES
FOR THE SECOND TIME!
I'M THE SAME AS YOU.
WITH MY HANDS,
I KILLED YOU ONCE BEFORE.
IN THAT ATTACK,
I KILLED THE OTHER YOU.
HALLELUJAH.
Peries:
I GAVE YOU THIS SCAR.
NO! SOMA PERIES DID THAT TO ME!
IT'S THE SAME WITH YOU.
BECAUSE I'M PERIES, TOO.
THAT'S WHY...
I'M SORRY, I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT I SHOULD DO.
AND I FEEL THE SAME WAY MARIE!
WHEN I FOUND OUT THAT
YOU WERE SOMA PERIES,
I COULDN'T STOP
THINKING ABOUT YOU,
I WANTED TO SAVE YOU SO MUCH!
BUT, NOW THAT I'VE DONE IT,
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I'M SUPPOSED TO DO NEXT.
SOMEONE LIKE ME
DOESN'T REALLY HAVE ANYTHING
TO OFFER YOU.
I'M JUST SO HAPPY
THAT YOU'RE HERE WITH ME.
MARIE.
JUST THINK I'M FINALLY
ABLE TO MEET YOU.
WHEN I WAS DEPRIVED
OF MY SENSES,
ALL I COULD DO WAS CALL OUT
WITH QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES.
AND YOU WERE THE ONLY ONE
WHO ANSWERED.
BECAUSE OF YOU,
I WAS ABLE TO FEEL GRATEFUL
FOR BEING ALIVE.
AND NOW I CAN
SEE YOU WITH MY OWN EYES,
I CAN SPEAK WITH YOU,
EVEN TOUCH YOU.
I NEVER THOUGHT
THIS DAY WOULD COME.
MARIE.
FOR ALL THIS,
I THANK GOD.
ALLELUJAH.
HUH?
THE FEDERATION?
I KNOW THAT MACHINE.
LIEUTENANT!
COLONEL!
SOMEONE YOU KNOW?
HUH?
THAT VOICE.
Allelujah:
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
EVERYONE,
MOVE TO THE CENTRAL BLOCK!
HIS VOICE.
HE'S A YOUNG MAN.
I SEE.
YOU'RE THAT YOUNG GUNDAM PILOT
FROM BACK THEN.
MOVE AWAY FROM THE LIEUTENANT!
CELESTIAL BEING!
I'M GLAD TO SEE YOU, KLAUS!
SORRY TO TELL YOU,
BUT THE ENEMY GOT
THE THIRD BRANCH.
RIGHT NOW, LET'S JUST
BE HAPPY THAT WE CAN MEET.
THAT ASIDE, IT LOOKS LIKE
THE FEDERATION
IS FINALLY MOVING IN
ON THE MIDDLE EAST.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
AFTER AZADISTAN WAS ATTACKED,
THE REGULAR FEDERATION FORCES
MARCHED RIGHT IN
AND SET UP
A PROVISIONAL GOVERNMENT.
PROVISIONAL GOVERNMENT?
REALLY?
IS THIS TRUE?!
(Surprised gasp)
PRINCESS MARINA ISMAIL!
IS WHAT YOU SAID TRUE?
IS AZADISTAN...
UNFORTUNATELY, IT IS TRUE.
THE FEDERATION IS USING THAT
PROVISIONAL GOVERNMENT
AS A PRECEDENT FOR
DISMANTLING THE OTHER NATIONS.
THEY'RE REORGANIZING
THE MIDDLE EAST.
DISMANTLING.
REORGANIZING THE MIDDLE EAST.
RIGHT NOW,
THERE IS NO SUCH PLACE
AS AZADISTAN.
(Shocked gasp)
OH!
(Gasps)
MARINA!
IT CAN'T BE.
(Sobs)
AZADISTAN...
(Growls)
(Grunts)
YOU SAY, HER PERSONALITY
WAS OVERWRITTEN?
THAT'S RIGHT.
BUT RIGHT NOW,
I'M NO LONGER SOMA PERIES.
I'M MARIE.
MARIE PARFACY.
MARIE.
SO, THAT'S YOUR REAL NAME,
LIEUTENANT?
THE SUPERHUMAN INSTITUTE
DID THIS TO YOU?!
MARIE IS A KIND HEARTED GIRL.
SHE'S NEVER BEEN
THE TYPE WHO WOULD KILL.
I'M NEVER GOING TO
HAND HER OVER TO YOU.
IF SHE GOES BACK TO
THE FEDERATION OR THE A‐LAWS,
THEY'LL USE HER
AS A SUPER SOLDIER!
BUT YOU'RE A MEMBER OF
CELESTIAL BEING, BOY.
EVEN IF SHE GOES WITH YOU,
SHE'LL STILL BE
DRAWN INTO THE FIGHTING.
I WON'T LET THAT HAPPEN!
TOO BAD FOR YOU,
I'M NOT STUPID ENOUGH
TO BELIEVE THE WORDS OF
A TERRORIST!
PLEASE, BELIEVE ME!
(Worried gasp)
BECAUSE OF WHAT YOU'VE DONE,
NO, BECAUSE OF THE CRAP
ALL YOU GUYS HAVE DONE,
I'VE LOST A LOT OF COUNTRYMEN
AND SOME GOOD SUBORDINATES.
DO YOU THINK I CAN FORGET
MY RESENTMENT SO EASILY?
PLEASE, COLONEL, DON'T!
THEN JUST SHOOT ME.
ALLELUJAH.
IN RETURN,
PROMISE ME THAT MARIE,
NO, SOMA PERIES,
WILL LIVE A NORMAL LIFE
AND NEVER BE INVOLVED IN
ANY FIGHTING AGAIN.
Peries:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
ALLELUJAH?
Allelujah:
IT'S ALL RIGHT, MARIE.
AS LONG AS YOU CAN LIVE
A HAPPY LIFE.
(Gasps)
PLEASE, SHOOT ME.
(Scared gasp)
REQUEST ACKNOWLEDGED.
(Screams)
NO!
MARIE!
(Gasps)
COLONEL?
A MOMENT AGO,
LIEUTENANT SOMA PERIES
DIED AN HONORABLE DEATH
IN BATTLE.
NOW, I'LL RETURN AND
INFORM MY SUPERIORS
OF HER FATE.
COLONEL.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
I NEVER DID THANK YOU.
HUH?
FIVE YEARS AGO, THE ACCIDENT
AT THE LOW ORBITAL STATION.
I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR YOUR PARTICIPATION
IN THE RESCUE EFFORT.
Peries:
COLONEL SMIRNOV!
YOU ONLY EVER SENT ME OUT
ON ANTI‐GUNDAM OPERATIONS.
FOR THAT, AND FOR NOT USING ME
IN ANY OTHER FIGHTING,
I WANT TO THANK YOU.
THE WAY YOU SAY IT.
NOW I'M ABSOLUTELY POSITIVE
YOU'RE NOT THE LIEUTENANT
I USED TO KNOW.
AND ONE MORE THING.
THE SOMA PERIES
WHO'S INSIDE ME
WANTS YOU TO KNOW SOMETHING.
MORE THAN ANYTHING,
I WANTED TO BE YOUR DAUGHTER.
IS THAT RIGHT?
THOSE WORDS ARE
MORE THAN ENOUGH FOR ME.
(Sobs)
COLONEL!
LIVE ON.
KEEP ON LIVING.
HAPPILY, TOGETHER WITH HIM.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING
YOU DID FOR ME, COLONEL.
HMM.
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
I AM LIEUTENANT SOMA PERIES,
SUPER SOLDIER NUMBER ONE.
DISPATCHED FROM THE
SUPER‐HUMAN INSTITUTE LABS.
YOU ARE MUCH TOO YOUNG.
TIEREN TAOZI.
THIS WILL BE MY MOBILE SUIT.
Sergei:
OUR ACE IN THE HOLE
AGAINST THE GUNDAMS.
BUT, SHE'S STILL
JUST A CHILD, REALLY.
(Pilots cheering)
Sergei:
I GUESS THIS IS
YOUR FIRST TASTE,
ISN'T IT, LIEUTENANT?
THIS IS THE SWEET TASTE
OF VICTORY.
THE SWEET TASTE OF VICTORY.
Sergei:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
NEVER MIND ABOUT ME!
KEEP FIGHTING, LIEUTENANT!
Peries:
I CAN'T!
HUH?
IF YOU WERE GONE, COLONEL,
I'D BE ALL ALONE.
MARIE?
(Peries crying)
THANK YOU FOR BEING ALIVE
AFTER ALL THIS TIME.
AND MOST OF ALL,
THANK YOU FOR
GIVING ME A REASON TO LIVE.
ALLELUJAH.
IF HE FELL IN THE WATER,
THERE'S NO WAY WE'LL FIND HIM.
ENEMY APPROACHING!
ENEMY?!
REGULAR FORCES.
HUH,
A LIGHT SIGNAL?!
WHAT IS HE...
PERIES.
ALLELUJAH DETECTED!
WHAT THE HELL?
ALL THIS TROUBLE
TRYING TO FIND HIM
AND HE'S HANGING OUT
WITH SOME GIRL?
(Chuckles)
WAY TO GO, PAL.
♪
Mileina:
IT'S A SIGNAL FROM HARO!
THEY FOUND MR. HAPTISM!
Feldt:
WE'VE FOUND ALLELUJAH!
ALLELUJAH.
LOOK AT THAT.
YOU'RE SMILING.
ANYBODY CAN SMILE
IF YOU GIVE THEM
SOMETHING TO BE HAPPY ABOUT.
MISS SUMERAGI!
YES. IT'S GREAT NEWS.
THIS IS A HUGE RELIEF TO ME,
ALLELUJAH.
I DON'T NEED TO
LOSE MY REASON FOR FIGHTING.
OOOOH!
LOOKS LIKE ALLELUJAH'S
GOT HIMSELF A GIRLFRIEND!
HE'S GOT A GIRLFRIEND?!
HOW'D THAT HAPPEN?!
WHAT THE HECK DOES THAT BOY
THINK HE'S DOING?!
Tieria:
I SEE.
SO ALLELUJAH HAPTISM'S
BEEN FOUND THEN.
Regene:
YES, THAT IS GOOD NEWS.
(Surprised gasp)
WHO'S THERE?!
HOW DID YOU KNOW
I WAS HERE?
I KNEW
BECAUSE WE'RE THE SAME.
(Stunned gasp)
WHY...
WHY DO YOU...
WHY DO YOU LOOK
JUST LIKE ME?!
IT'S BECAUSE WE HAVE
THE EXACT SAME DNA.
BASE SEQUENCE PATTERN
0988 TYPE.
THAT MEANS YOU ARE...
AN INNOVATOR.
REGENE REGETTA.
YOU'RE AN INNOVATOR!
Narrator:
TIERIA ERDE. RIBBONS ALMARK.
THE TWO REFORMING INNOVATORS
FINALLY MEET.
NEXT EPISODE:
"TWISTEDNESS OF INNOCENCE".
AEOLIA'S PLAN IS ACCELERATED.