Secretary General:
IT HAS BEEN FOUR MONTHS
SINCE "BREAK PILLAR",
THE UNPRECEDENTED ACT OF
MEGA‐TERRORISM
BY ANTI‐FEDERATION FORCES.
COUNTLESS VICTIMS AND
THEIR FAMILIES
ARE STILL STRUGGLING TO COPE
WITH THIS TRAGEDY.
HOWEVER, THANKS TO
THE MEMENTO MORI,
THE COMPLETE COLLAPSE OF
THE ORBITAL ELEVATOR
WAS AVERTED.
WE ARE ALSO SEEING
THE UNUSUAL WEATHER
CAUSED BY THE DISASTER
BEGINNING TO SUBSIDE.
AND SO TODAY,
HUMANITY WELCOMES
A NEW DAY OF REVIVAL!
THANKS TO TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE
FROM FEDERATION MEMBER STATES,
THE SUPPLY OF POWER FROM AFRICA
TOWER HAS BEEN REESTABLISHED!
(Cheering)
ON THIS JOYOUS DAY,
AS THE FIRST PRESIDENT OF
THE EARTH SPHERE FEDERATION,
I MAKE THIS SOLEMN VOW!
CONCURRENTLY WITH THIS REVIVAL,
A NEW BATTLE BEGINS TODAY!
TO PREVENT FURTHER ACTS
OF TERRORISM,
THE COMMAND STRUCTURE
OF THE FEDERATION FORCES
WILL BE MERGED WITH
THE AUTONOMOUS PEACEKEEPING
FORCE, THE A‐LAWS.
WE WILL ERADICATE
THE DISSIDENT ELEMENTS,
AND FOCUS ALL OF OUR EFFORTS
TOWARDS CREATING
A TRUE UNITED WORLD!
(Cheering and applause)
I TAKE IT YOU STILL
CAN'T FIND OUT
WHAT'S BECOME OF
COLONEL MANNEQUIN?
WE'VE ADDED MORE SECURITY
PERSONNEL, BUT NOTHING YET.
HMM?
ARE YOU SURE? CELESTIAL BEING
HAS MADE AN APPEARANCE IN SPACE?
WHAT'S THEIR
INTENDED TARGET?!
THEY'RE GOING
FOR THE ORBITAL RING.
MEMENTO MORI STATION NUMBER TWO.
Tieria:
I'M CLEARING A PATH!
Allelujah:
THE A‐LAWS ARE ALWAYS
TOUGH DEFENDERS!
IN THAT CASE...
MARIE!
ALLELUJAH,
GIVE HER SOME SUPPORT!
ROGER THAT!
HOW ARE THE GENERATOR CONTROLS?
I'M ON IT!
(Thinking)
I'M ONLY HELPING THEM
THIS ONCE.
AS LONG AS IT'S TO DESTROY
THE SATELLITE WEAPON...
HUH?
IT'S ALL LINKED UP!
Setsuna:
ROGER!
TRANS AM...
RAISER!
(Aggressive yell)
♪
Katharon Leader #1:
SO, CELESTIAL BEING DESTROYED
THE SATELLITE WEAPON.
Katharon Leader #2:
MAYBE NOW, THE A‐LAWS WILL TURN
THEIR ATTENTION TO SPACE.
THEY'RE GONNA EASE UP
ON THE SEARCH FOR US.
THIS IS OUR CHANCE TO‐‐
(Gasps)
Katharon Leader #2:
AN AUTOMATON!
Katharon Leader #1:
RUN!
(Rapid gunfire)
(Boys chanting)
WE WANT FOOD! WE WANT FOOD!
BOY, WHAT TERRIBLE
MANNERS!
AWFUL!
YOU CAN CALM DOWN NOW,
IT'S FINALLY READY.
(Amazed gasps)
David:
THAT LOOKS GREAT!
Leanne:
YOU HAVE TO HELP US SERVE THIS!
Yael:
THAT'S RIGHT!
I WONDER HOW LONG WE'LL BE ABLE
TO STAY HIDDEN HERE.
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT INCIDENT
AT THE ORBITAL ELEVATOR
HIT OUR FORCES PRETTY HARD.
I'D LIKE TO STAY HERE
UNTIL WE REGROUP.
IS THAT POSSIBLE GIVEN
HOW THE A‐LAWS
ARE TIGHTENING UP
THEIR SURVEILLANCE?
WELL, WE'VE GOT
CELESTIAL BEING.
BUT WE CAN'T COUNT ON THEM
ALL THE TIME.
BUT SOMEBODY HAS TO DO
SOMETHING.
OR ELSE NOTHING
WILL EVER CHANGE.
I'M SCARED,
KLAUS.
I FEEL LIKE ALL OF US
ARE CAUGHT UP IN SOME WHIRLPOOL
THAT'S TOO ENORMOUS TO ESCAPE.
SHIRIN.
♪
♪ IN THIS LIFE WE LOSE THINGS ♪
♪ JUST SO THEY MIGHT BE FOUND ♪
THIS IS THE SONG
MARINA AND THE CHILDREN DID.
WHY IS IT BEING
PLAYED ON THE RADIO?
♪ AND PART WAYS JUST TO KNOW ♪
♪ WE MIGHT MEET AGAIN ♪
♪ WE SAY GOODBYE BUT WE KNOW ♪
♪ WE'LL SOON BE SAYING HELLO ♪
♪ IN THIS WAY, ALL WE LOSE ♪
♪ WILL COME BACK AROUND ♪
(Sighs)
HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
AH...NOTHING.
MARIE!
HOW MANY TIMES DO I HAVE TO
TELL YOU TO STOP THAT?
I'M SOMA PERIES,
SUPER SOLDIER NUMBER ONE
OF THE SUPERHUMAN INSTITUTE!
WHOA!
MARIE.
Peries (in memory):
COLONEL.
(Screaming)
COLONEL!
(Sobbing)
(Screaming)
(Grunts)
WHY?
WHY THE HELL DID THE COLONEL
HAVE TO DIE LIKE THAT?
HUH?
THAT'S LIEUTENANT ANDREI'S GN‐X.
HE WAS THE ONE WHO KILLED HIM?
HIS FLESH AND BLOOD,
HIS VERY OWN FATHER.
MARIE, WHAT'S WRONG?
SHUT UP! MY NAME'S SOMA!
SOMA PERIES!
(Thinking)
HOW COULD YOU JUST THROW AWAY
SOMETHING I COULD NEVER HAVE?
NO MATTER HOW BADLY
I WANTED IT?
HOW?
I PROMISED THE COLONEL I WOULD
NEVER LET HER FIGHT AGAIN.
AND I LET HIM DOWN.
JUST GIVE HER SOME SPACE
FOR A WHILE.
ALL SHE NEEDS IS
A LITTLE BIT OF TIME
TO GET HER FEELINGS
STRAIGHTENED OUT.
BUT I DON'T WANT HER
RISKING HERSELF!
Lyle:
YOU HAVE TO STOP
TRYING TO CONTROL HER.
IF YOU REALLY CARE ABOUT HER,
THEN TRY TO UNDERSTAND HER.
YOU HAVE TO ACCEPT THAT
SHE FEELS DRIVEN TO FIGHT.
(Sighs)
HMM.
I WONDER IF IT'S THE SAME
WITH LOUISE.
TURNING THE GRIEF OF
LOSING HER FAMILY INTO HATRED.
WHATEVER COULD I SAY TO HER?
Sumeragi:
HOW'S SETSUNA'S CONDITION?
WE'RE SEEING MORE
REGENERATION DEFECTS
IN THE CELLS AROUND
HIS SHOULDER INJURY.
THE EFFECTS OF
PSEUDO GN PARTICLES.
HOWEVER, THEY SEEM TO BE
SPREADING EXTREMELY SLOWLY.
THIS IS VERY DIFFERENT FROM
MR. LASSE'S CONDITION.
IT MEANS SOMETHING IS WORKING
TO SUPPRESS THE DAMAGE.
TIMES LIKE THIS,
I WISH I COULD ACCESS VEDA.
THIS IS A SCHEME BY
ALI AL‐SAACHEZ.
NO, BY THE INNOVATORS WHO WANT
TO GET THEIR HANDS ON 00.
WHICH MEANS THEY DON'T HAVE
ANY INFORMATION
ON THE TWIN DRIVE.
MY GUNDAM IS OUR TRUMP CARD.
I HEAR CELESTIAL BEING HAS
FINALLY RESUMED ITS ACTIVITIES.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME
THEY DID.
TO BE QUITE HONEST,
I'M DISAPPOINTED
WITH THE CURRENT SITUATION.
HOW SO?
INFORMATION CONTROL
AND MILITARY EXPANSION.
YOU'VE APPLIED THE METHODS OF
PREVIOUS ERAS ON A GLOBAL SCALE.
WHAT ARE YOU
PLANNING TO DO NEXT?
NOTHING HUMANS
NEED TO KNOW ABOUT.
BUT ISN'T YOUR PLAN
TO EVENTUALLY
MAKE ALL OF HUMANITY
INTO INNOVATORS?
NO, NOT AT ALL.
(Gasps)
IN AN AGE OF REFORMATION,
BOTH THE OBSOLETE AND
THE WICKED MUST BE THROWN AWAY.
FOR INSTANCE, THOSE INDIVIDUALS
WITH AN OLD‐FASHIONED MINDSET,
WHO TAKE WEALTH AND POWER
FOR GRANTED
AND LOOK DOWN ON THE MASSES,
EVEN THOUGH
THEY'RE OF THE SAME KIND.
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ME
PERSONALLY?
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT,
TIME WILL LEAVE YOU BEHIND.
SIMILAR TO THE WAY
THAT YOUR BEAUTY
WILL WITHER AWAY WITH TIME.
IN ORDER TO CLING
TO THE GLORIOUS PAST,
PEOPLE ACHIEVE PEACE
BY HURTING OTHERS.
PEOPLE KNOW IT ISN'T
THE RIGHT THING TO DO,
BUT THEY'RE UNABLE
TO STOP ANY OF IT.
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE THAT SOMEONE
NEEDS TO TEACH THEM A LESSON?
AND YOU FEEL
YOU'RE THE ONES TO DO IT?
HUMAN VALUES ARE
FAR TOO LIMITED.
WE CONSIDER THINGS FROM
A MUCH BROADER PERSPECTIVE.
IS THAT RIGHT?
WELL THEN,
HERE'S TO THAT
BROADER REFORMATION.
I LOOK FORWARD TO IT.
LET ME JUST TELL YOU
ONE THING.
YOU CAN NEVER
BECOME AN INNOVATOR.
(Gasps)
SAD AS IT IS,
I'M MERELY TELLING YOU
THE TRUTH.
Regene:
ARE YOU SURE THAT'S WISE?
PUSHING HER AWAY LIKE THAT?
I NO LONGER HAVE
ANY USE FOR HER.
BUT IF YOU WANT,
YOU CAN LOOK AFTER HER.
HEAVENS, NO.
BUT OVER
THE PAST FOUR MONTHS,
YOU HAVE MET WITH HER
QUITE OFTEN.
HMPH.
I WAS COLLECTING INFORMATION
FROM HER ABOUT CELESTIAL BEING.
OH REALLY?
FINE THEN,
LET'S JUST LEAVE IT AT THAT.
(Angry growl)
I HEARD THAT YOU WERE PROMOTED
TO FIRST LIEUTENANT.
YEAH, IT SEEMS THAT THEY WERE
ABLE TO CONFIRM THAT
THE MACHINE I SHOT DOWN DURING
THE "BREAK PILLAR" INCIDENT
BELONGED TO THE RINGLEADER OF
THE WHOLE COUP D'ÉTAT.
AND SO THE TOP BRASS
REWARDED ME FOR IT.
CONGRATULATIONS, LIEUTENANT.
I HAVE TO SAY, BEING
CONGRATULATED BY YOU IS‐‐
Revive:
WELL, A PROMOTION FOR
KILLING YOUR OWN FATHER.
THE A‐LAWS ARE REALLY
AN ELITE GROUP,
YOU SHOW
A LOT OF PROMISE.
WHERE DID YOU HEAR THAT?
Louise:
IS IT TRUE, LIEUTENANT?
YOU KILLED YOUR OWN FATHER?
(Sighs)
I HAD NO CHOICE,
HE WAS A REBEL SYMPATHIZER.
ALL I DID WAS PERFORM MY DUTY
AS A SOLDIER.
YOU KNEW IT WAS YOUR FATHER
AND YOU STILL KILLED HIM?!
BUT WHY?!
FOR PEACE!
FOR ALL THE PEOPLE WHO ARE
PRAYING FOR AN END TO WAR!
THOSE WHO SPLIT FROM
THE MILITARY
TO THREATEN THE GOVERNMENT
MUST FACE JUDGMENT.
AS HIS OWN FLESH AND BLOOD,
I THOUGHT IT WAS
AN ACT OF KINDNESS
THAT I BE THE ONE TO BURY HIM.
BUT THAT'S...
I MEAN, THAT'S JUST...
WELL, WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE DONE
IN THE SAME SITUATION?
(Gasps)
I'M NOT SURE.
SO YOU CAN TAKE
THE LIFE OF STRANGERS,
BUT NOT THAT OF
A BLOOD RELATIVE?!
(Sighs)
(Hiling laughs)
HUH?
A MAN WHO KILLED HIS FATHER,
AND A WOMAN SEEKING REVENGE
FOR HER FAMILY.
YOU'RE PERFECT FOR EACH OTHER!
(Grunts)
WELL, IF SHE'S
THAT IMPORTANT TO YOU,
DO YOUR BEST TO PROTECT HER.
LISTEN.
WE'RE FIGHTING FOR OUR IDEALS,
WARRANT OFFICER.
TO ACHIEVE THEM,
SOMETIMES WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
MAKE TOUGH CHOICES.
(Gasps)
ONE DAY, YOU'LL BE IN
THAT SITUATION.
I WONDER IF I CAN DO IT.
TO HIM.
WILL I BE ABLE TO FIRE AT SAJI?
Saji:
I HAVE TO.
Setsuna:
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO
GET LOUISE HALEVY BACK,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO FIGHT.
YOU'LL JUST BE FIGHTING
TO BRING HER BACK.
Saji:
THAT'S MY BATTLE.
SO THE A‐LAWS HAVE FINALLY TAKEN
OVER THE FEDERATION FORCES.
IN THE PAST FOUR MONTHS ALONE,
WE'VE COME UNDER ATTACK
FROM THE A‐LAWS OVER 20 TIMES.
THINGS JUST KEEP
GETTING WORSE FOR US!
YOU KNOW WHAT,
I'M STARTING TO THINK
THE ENEMY KNOWS
OUR EXACT POSITION AT ALL TIMES.
Mileina:
IT JUST KEEPS GETTING WORSE!
SUMERAGI LEE NORIEGA,
PERHAPS IT'S TIME
WE PUT THAT PLAN
WE DISCUSSED INTO ACTION.
WHAT'S THE PLAN ABOUT?
ABOUT VEDA.
YOU SEE,
WE'VE CONCLUDED THAT
THE FEDERATION, OR RATHER,
THE INNOVATORS HAVE BEEN USING
VEDA TO CONTROL INFORMATION.
IF WE CAN TAKE VEDA BACK...
BUT THERE'S NOT THAT MUCH
WE CAN DO
WITHOUT KNOWING WHERE VEDA'S
LOCATED NOW, IS THERE?
Setsuna:
IN WHICH CASE,
WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO ASK SOMEONE
WHO HAS THAT INFORMATION.
Lasse:
WHAT? YOU MEAN AN INNOVATOR!
THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
HMM.
Anew:
HEY, LYLE,
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
ABOUT WHAT?
I WANNA KNOW MORE
ABOUT YOUR BROTHER.
I DON'T REMEMBER HIM SO WELL.
WHEN I WAS IN JUNIOR SCHOOL,
I MOVED TO THE DORMITORIES.
WHY'D YOU LIVE IN A DORMITORY?
Lyle:
BECAUSE I COULDN'T STAND BEING
COMPARED TO MY GIFTED BROTHER.
RATHER THAN FIGHTING IT,
I CHOSE TO RUN AWAY.
Anew:
BUT YOU BECAME A GUNDAM MEISTER,
JUST LIKE HIM.
HMPH.
OUR MOTIVES WERE VERY DIFFERENT.
HEY, SPEAKING OF
FAMILY AND SUCH,
WHAT ABOUT YOURS, ANEW?
MY FAMILY?
YEAH.
(Sighs)
WELL, I...
THAT'S KINDA...
HMM.
(Lyle sighs)
IT'S OKAY, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE HERE RIGHT NOW, ANEW.
AND THAT'S
ALL I NEED TO KNOW.
LYLE.
(Gasps)
(Grunts)
WHAT THE?
ANEW.
ANEW, ANEW!
ANEW!
(Gasps)
UH...
WHAT DID I...
DON'T FADE OUT LIKE THAT
WHEN WE'RE KISSING!
OH, SORRY.
ENEMY SHIP LOCATED.
INFORM THE FLEET.
THAT'S OUR DEAR REVIVE!
YOU'RE LIKE A DOG
SNIFFING OUT A BONE!
WHAT WAS THAT?
JUST EXPRESSING MY GRATITUDE.
Liu Mei:
HAVE YOU HEARD
FROM NENA TRINITY?
Hong Long:
NOTHING YET.
USELESS LITTLE GIRL.
(Gasps)
MY MISTRESS.
THIS IS IT!
HUH?
DEAR BROTHER,
SET THE SHIP'S COURSE
FOR THE PTOLEMAIOS!
Operator:
INCOMING TRANSMISSION FROM
CAPTAIN REVIVAL, SIR.
CELESTIAL BEING HAS BEEN
LOCATED AT POINT ES‐8874.
GIVE THE ORDER TO SEND OUT
THE MOBILE SUIT TEAMS.
ASK THOSE TWO LICENSE HOLDERS
FOR THEIR HELP AS WELL.
ROGER!
Announcer:
MOBILE SUIT TEAMS,
PREPARE TO LAUNCH!
I FINALLY GET TO PILOT AN AHEAD.
HMM.
ALL FUNCTIONS NORMAL.
NOW CONNECTING GN DRIVE.
(Metal clanking)
Announcer:
OPENING HATCH!
I'M READY TO FIGHT.
I WILL FIGHT.
Andrei:
AHEAD TEAM ONE, LAUNCHING.
ROGER!
HALEVY UNIT, TAKING OFF!
IT'S BEEN FINE‐TUNED
TO PERFECTION.
I'VE EVEN IMPROVED THAT SYSTEM
YOU CALL "THE SECRET".
THEREFORE‐‐
DON'T SAY IT.
I KNOW WHAT HAS TO BE DONE.
Feldt:
VISUAL SENSORS ARE DETECTING
MOBILE SUIT TEAMS!
0054 UNTIL THEY ENTER
COMBAT AIRSPACE.
WE HAVE PROBLEMS, PEOPLE!
Mileina:
ENEMIES APPROACHING!
SHORT AND SWEET,
JUST DO WHAT YOU ALWAYS DO!
Feldt:
MILEINA, THAT'S TOO CASUAL!
SETSUNA,
HOW'S YOUR SHOULDER FEELING?
HMM,
IT'S DOING ALL RIGHT.
Lyle:
ANEW.
HMM? WHAT'S UP?
NEVER MIND.
IT'S NOTHING IMPORTANT.
(Gasps)
ARE YOU HEADING OUT?
YES, OF COURSE.
OKAY THEN.
WHAT'S THE SITUATION?
WE'VE DETECTED A TOTAL OF 12
A‐LAWS MOBILE SUITS APPROACHING.
THAT'S SURPRISINGLY LOW.
DON'T LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
THIS IS OUR CHANCE!
THERE'S AN INNOVATOR
AMONG THE ENEMY FORCES!
(Gasps)
SO, SAJI CROSSROAD.
I NOTICED THAT LOUISE'S MACHINE
IS WITH THE A‐LAWS FORCES.
WE'VE BEEN RUNNING AWAY FROM THE
ENEMY FOR THE LAST FOUR MONTHS
TO RECOVER
OUR FIGHTING STRENGTH.
BUT WE'RE GONNA STAND AND
FIGHT NOW, AREN'T WE?
YEAH.
ARE YOU GONNA SHOOT LOUISE DOWN?
THAT'S UP TO YOU.
HUH?
DESTRUCTION ISN'T THE ONLY THING
THAT BATTLES CAN BRING.
THEY CAN ALSO CREATE THINGS.
I BELIEVE IT'S POSSIBLE.
I THINK OUR GUNDAMS ARE CAPABLE
OF DOING THAT.
THE REST IS UP TO YOU.
LISTEN,
I CAN'T PULL A TRIGGER.
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
ALL I CAN DO IS
KEEP TRYING TO REACH LOUISE.
I UNDERSTAND.
BUT EVEN SO,
I'LL TRY...
I'LL TRY.
LET'S GO SEE LOUISE HALEVY.
(Sighs)
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY!
Feldt:
OPENING PTOLEMY'S FIRST,
SECOND, AND THIRD HATCHES!
Mileina:
MR. ERDE, GOOD LUCK
IN YOUR BATTLE TODAY!
Tieria:
ROGER THAT!
SERAVEE, AND TIERIA ERDE,
LAUNCHING!
Allelujah:
YOU ALL SET?
ANYTIME'S GOOD.
JUST DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
I WILL PROTECT YOU, MARIE.
ARCHER ARIOS,
ALLELUJAH HAPTISM
WITH SOMA PERIES!
COMMENCING INTERCEPTION!
Lyle:
ANEW, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
I LOVE YOU.
(Gasps)
(Cheering)
HE'S TARGETED AND FIRING,
ALL RIGHT!
WAIT, WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN?
THAT'S AWESOME! THE FLOWERS
OF LOVE HAVE BLOSSOMED!
CONGRATULATIONS ANEW!
(Embarrassed gasps)
JUST GO, ALREADY!
ALL RIGHT!
CHERUDIM, AND LOCKON STRATOS,
TARGETED AND FIRING!
Setsuna:
WE'RE GONNA GO SEE HER, SAJI.
Saji:
YEAH! LET'S GO, SETSUNA!
00, SETSUNA F. SEIEI,
LAUNCHING!
0 RAISER, SAJI CROSSROAD,
I'M TAKING OFF!
LOUISE.
SAJI.
MOTHER.
COLONEL.
MARIE.
ANEW.
VEDA.
GUNDAM!
COMMENCE MISSION!
♪
(Panting)
(Children laughing)
KLAUS, RUN FOR IT!
THE SECURITY FORCES
ARE RIGHT‐‐
KENNY!
(Gasps)
Marina:
WE'RE IN DANGER! COME HERE!
TAKE THE CHILDREN
AND GET OUT!
(Gasps)
JOSEPH! NO, DON'T!
MARINA!
(Gunshot)
Regene:
PLEASE GIVE THIS INFORMATION
TO THEM DIRECTLY.
THESE ARE THE COORDINATES
FOR VEDA!
Narrator:
THE BRILLIANT LIGHT
FROM THE TRANS‐AM RAISER
ALLOWS THE SEPARATED COUPLE
TO COME TOGETHER,
AND FACE EACH OTHER ON
THE BATTLEFIELD.
NEXT EPISODE:
"SHADOW OF THE INNOVATORS".
THE DARK SCHEMER GETS
IN THE WAY OF PEOPLE IN LOVE.