WASN'T THERE
SOME OTHER WAY?
THERE WASN'T.
SEE, AT THAT MOMENT,
SHE...
SHE WAS SOMEONE ELSE,
NOT ANEW.
BUT HOW CAN YOU
BE CERTAIN OF THAT?
IT'S HARD TO EXPLAIN.
BUT I WAS ABSOLUTELY
SURE OF IT.
IF I HADN'T ACTED,
LYLE DYLANDY WOULD BE DEAD.
Saji:
REALLY?
IT'S THE SAME WITH
LOUISE HALEVY.
I CAN SENSE SOMETHING
HAS TAKEN HOLD OF HER.
I FEEL THESE THINGS.
THERE'S BEEN SOMETHING
A LITTLE ODD ABOUT YOU LATELY,
LIKE MAYBE
SOMETHING'S CHANGED.
Feldt:
WE'RE CHECKING
THE SHIPBOARD SYSTEMS
SO WE'RE SHUTTING DOWN
THE POWER FOR A MOMENT.
(Startled gasp)
Mileina:
CHECK COMPLETED.
NOW RESTORING
NORMAL SHIP POWER.
RESTORING NAVIGATION SYSTEM.
EVERYTHING'S ALL GREEN.
ANY SIGN OF AN ENEMY FLEET,
MILEINA?
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE THERE'S
ANYTHING IN VISIBLE RANGE.
Tieria:
STAY ALERT.
THEY MIGHT TRY
SOME DESPICABLE TRICK
LIKE THEY DID
THE LAST TIME.
TIERIA.
(Gasps)
HMM.
MISS SUMERAGI,
IT LOOKS LIKE
WE MIGHT'VE RECEIVED
AN URGENT CODED MESSAGE
WHILE THE SYSTEM
WAS DOWN.
WHAT'S IT SAY?
ALL IT CONTAINS ARE
COORDINATES IN SPACE.
Feldt:
THE POINT IS LAGRANGE FIVE.
IT'S ECLIPSE,
AN UNFINISHED COLONY WHERE
CONSTRUCTION WAS SUSPENDED.
(Gasping)
MY MISTRESS.
I'M JUST FINE.
I CAN STILL DO IT.
I HAVE TO.
♪
Tieria:
WE'RE GOING TO LAGRANGE FIVE?
WE'RE RESPONDING TO SOMEONE
WHO SENT US NOTHING
BUT COORDINATES IN SPACE?
THAT'S BOTHERING ME, TOO.
IT'S BECAUSE SETSUNA INSISTS
ON GOING THERE TO CHECK IT OUT.
SETSUNA DOES?
HMM.
I'M IN FAVOR, TOO.
Sumeragi:
IAN?
Ian:
LINDA AND THE OTHERS
WHO ESCAPED WITH HER
ARE CONTINUING THEIR RESEARCH
AT LAGRANGE FIVE.
IF EVERYTHING'S ON TRACK,
WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO PICK UP
THE NEW EQUIPMENT.
AND IT'LL GIVE US MORE TIME
TO REPAIR THE GUNDAMS
AS WE TRAVEL THERE.
HMM.
ROGER THAT.
YOU WANT ME TO TAKE OVER
AS HELMSMAN OF THE SHIP?!
LASSE'S STILL RECOVERING.
SOMEONE HAS TO TAKE OVER
THE JOB OF PROTECTING PTOLEMY.
YOU'RE JUST TRYING TO
KEEP ME OFF THE BATTLEFIELD.
THIS IS ABOUT THE PROMISE
I MADE TO COLONEL SMIRNOV.
PLEASE,
LISTEN TO ME.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
SOMA PERIES!
IF YOU KEEP FIGHTING THIS WAY,
YOU'RE GONNA BE KILLED TOO.
(Gasps)
PTOLEMY WILL TAKE A DETOUR AND
DRAW THE ENEMY'S ATTENTION.
IN THE MEANTIME,
PLEASE GET IN TOUCH WITH
THE PERSON WHO CONTACTED US.
ROGER THAT.
CAN YOU COME?
IT'S TO HELP PEOPLE,
RIGHT?
I DON'T MIND HELPING OUT
ON STUFF LIKE THAT.
(Gasps)
SO, LYLE...
I REGRET
WHAT HAPPENED BEFORE.
MY EMOTIONS GOT THE BEST OF ME.
I FAILED AS A MEISTER.
LYLE, I JUST WANT TO‐‐
I'LL FIGHT!
OH YEAH, I'LL FIGHT.
ALL RIGHT THEN.
(Thinking)
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I'LL DESTROY
THOSE DAMNED INNOVATORS.
NOT FOR KATHARON, AND NOT FOR
CELESTIAL BEING.
I'LL DO IT OF MY OWN FREE WILL.
HOWEVER...
(Grunts)
HELP ME, NEIL.
Feldt:
OPENING PTOLEMY'S
FIRST AND THIRD HATCHES.
TRANSFERRING
LAUNCH TIMING TO DOUBLE 0.
ROGER.
SETSUNA F. SEIEI PILOTING
DOUBLE 0, LAUNCHING.
0 RAISER, SAJI CROSSROAD,
I'M TAKING OFF NOW!
Saji:
0 RAISER,
DOCKING MODE!
DOUBLE 0 RAISER NOW READY.
SETTING COURSE FOR LAGRANGE FIVE
AND HEADING OUT.
Operator:
OPTICAL SENSORS HAVE DETECTED
CELESTIAL BEING'S
SPACESHIP, SIR.
THEY'RE CHANGING DIRECTION.
MAKE SURE WE KEEP
FOLLOWING THEM.
ROGER. THIRD FLEET
NOW CHANGING COURSE.
IF WE CAN DEFEAT
CELESTIAL BEING,
THE OPPOSITION'S SPIRIT
WILL BE BROKEN.
WE CAN'T COUNT ON
THOSE LICENSE HOLDERS
AND THEIR PRIVATE AGENDAS.
WE'LL WIPE THEM OUT WITH
OVERWHELMING FORCE
JUST LIKE COMMANDER KATAGIRI
WOULD WANT US TO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
ANEW'S BEEN DEFEATED, AS WELL.
EVEN THOUGH
WE'RE INNOVATORS!
DOUBLE 0 GUNDAM.
YOU'RE MINE NOW!
DOUBLE 0!
(Gasps)
WHAT THE...?!
(Grunts)
GUNDAM!
(Screaming)
Revive: (Thinking)
THE WAY HE FIGHTS,
IT'S MORE THAN
JUST HIS MOBILE SUIT.
THE ONLY ANSWER IS THE
DOUBLE 0'S PILOT IS CHANGING.
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
THERE'S NO OTHER WAY TO
EXPLAIN WHAT HAPPENED.
ARE YOU TRYING TO TELL ME
THAT HE'S A PUREBRED TYPE?
COULD IT BE SETSUNA F. SEIEI?
WILL HE BE THE ONE TO BECOME
HUMANITY'S FIRST INNOVATOR?
(Gasping)
GUNDAM.
(Gulps)
AH, HERE YOU ARE,
WARRANT OFFICER.
YOUR NEW MOBILE ARMOR'S
REPAIRS ARE JUST‐‐
SHUT UP!
HUH?!
(Gasps)
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
WARRANT OFFICER,
WHAT'S WRONG?
I SAID,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT‐‐
(Gasps)
Graham:
HOPE I'M NOT INTERRUPTING.
MR. BUSHIDO.
WHAT IS IT?
THE WARRANT OFFICER AND I
HAVE BEEN GIVEN SPECIAL ORDERS.
GET READY TO SORTIE.
YES, SIR!
HMM?
PLEASE ALLOW ME TO
ACCOMPANY YOU, SIR!
I'LL GO AND GET PERMISSION
FROM GENERAL GOODMAN.
HMPH.
DO AS YOU WISH.
THOUGH I DON'T EXPECT
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
KEEP UP WITH MINE AND
THE WARRANT OFFICER'S MACHINES.
Setsuna:
IT'LL BE A FEW DAYS BEFORE
WE ARRIVE AT THE TARGET POINT.
YOU SHOULD GET SOME REST.
SOUNDS GOOD,
I'LL DO THAT.
THERE'S BEEN SOMETHING
A LITTLE ODD ABOUT YOU LATELY.
SETSUNA, YOU COULD CHANGE.
I COULDN'T,
SO YOU'LL HAVE TO DO IT FOR ME.
I THINK I UNDERSTAND.
I WILL...
MAKE THE CHANGE.
NO MATTER WHAT AWAITS ME
AT THE END.
(Birds chirping)
(Startled gasp)
OH, IT'S YOU.
(Grunts)
KLAUS! ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?!
YEAH, IT'S JUST A SCRATCH.
I WAS SO GLAD
YOU MADE IT OKAY.
Shirin:
GO UP INTO SPACE?
Klaus:
I MADE CONTACT WITH SURVIVORS
OF THE ATTEMPTED COUP
AGAINST THE FEDERATION.
WITH OUR BRANCH
NEARLY WIPED OUT,
IT'S DANGEROUS FOR US TO
REMAIN ON EARTH ANY LONGER.
YES,
BUT KATHARON DOESN'T HAVE
AS MUCH FIGHTING STRENGTH
IN SPACE.
ACTUALLY, I'M OPTIMISTIC.
THE REALITY IS, THERE ARE
MORE AND MORE PEOPLE
WHO ARE TRYING
TO FIND A WAY TO SPEAK OUT
ABOUT THEIR FEELINGS
IN A DIFFERENT WAY
FROM US AND CELESTIAL BEING.
(Marina's song playing)
YOU MEAN THIS SONG?
THAT'S RIGHT.
PRINCESS MARINA'S SONG IS
SPREADING AMONG THE PEOPLE.
Shirin:
MARINA'S SONG IS SPREADING
AROUND THE WORLD? WHY?
Klaus:
I BELIEVE THE PEOPLE ARE
WISHING FOR PEACE.
THEY WISH THAT THROUGH
PRINCESS MARINA'S SONG,
THE FIGHTING WILL STOP,
AND PEOPLE WILL BE ABLE
TO LIVE TOGETHER.
WE'VE BEEN SO FOCUSED
ON OPPOSITION,
WE MAY HAVE FORGOTTEN THAT
PEOPLE CAN STILL
UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER,
AND THAT PATH REMAINS AN OPTION.
♪
Shirin:
THAT BELIEF THAT WE CAN
UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER.
MARINA HAS ALWAYS
WISHED FOR THAT,
AND SHE BELIEVED IN
WHAT IT WOULD BRING.
♪
Hong Long:
NO ONE HAS SHOWED UP
AT THE DESIGNATED POINT, YET.
MY MISTRESS,
DO YOU REALLY THINK
CELESTIAL BEING WILL COME HERE?
RIGHT NOW,
I CAN'T SAY FOR CERTAIN.
BUT IF THEY DON'T APPEAR SOON,
THE WORLD WILL BELONG TO
THE INNOVATORS.
OR RATHER, IT'LL BELONG TO
RIBBONS ALMARK.
HOW LONG HAS NENA TRINITY BEEN
SIDING WITH THE INNOVATORS?
STOP ASKING ALL THESE QUESTIONS
AND THINK FOR YOURSELF!
IT'S BECAUSE OF YOUR FLAWS
THAT I WAS FORCED TO BECOME
THE HEAD OF THE WANG FAMILY!
HUH?!
YOUR INABILITY TO BE
THE HEAD OF THIS FAMILY
LED TO MY LIFE
BEING TWISTED LIKE THIS!
THAT'S THE REAL REASON WHY I
WANT TO SEE THE WORLD REFORMED!
EVEN IF I GIVE UP MY STATUS,
REPUTATION, AND WEALTH FOR IT.
YES.
I'LL START
MY LIFE AGAIN
AND OBTAIN A FUTURE
THAT'S JUST MINE!
YOU'RE STAYING WITH ME
UNTIL THE END, HONG LONG.
HUH?
THAT'S THE RESPONSIBILITY
YOU HAVE TO BEAR.
Nena:
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO BE
SO MELODRAMATIC?
YOU'RE PATHETIC.
JUST SHOWS HOW STUPID YOU ARE.
NENA TRINITY!
Nena:
I DESPISE YOU.
(Growls)
GOODBYE,
MY DEAR "MISTRESS".
LIU MEI!
(Gunshot)
Nena:
I DESPISE YOU.
(Growls)
GOODBYE,
MY DEAR "MISTRESS".
LIU MEI!
(Gunshot)
(Gasps)
(Grunting)
HONG LONG!
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
(Gunshots)
BROTHER!
(Grunts)
LIU MEI.
LIVE ON.
BROTHER, NO!
COME ON!
(Gasps)
YOU'RE IN MY WAY.
(Nena chuckles)
GOING OUT IN STYLE!
GOING AFTER HER?
WE DON'T HAVE TO.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
THAT'S CORRECT.
(Thinking)
WITH THIS,
THE PLAN WILL ACCELERATE.
NOT AEOLIA'S OR RIBBONS' PLAN,
BUT MY PLAN.
HE'S HERE.
Setsuna:
I CAN'T REACH THE DESIGNATED
POINT IN A MOBILE SUIT.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO PASS CONTROL
OF THE SUIT OVER TO YOU.
Saji:
ROGER.
(Door opens and closes)
IT'S JUST UP AHEAD.
(Setsuna gasps)
HUH?
(Gasps)
SETSUNA F. SEIEI,
YOU MADE IT.
WHAT'S GOING ON,
WANG LIU MEI?
ARE YOU INJURED?
NO, IT'S NOTHING REALLY.
BUT YOU SHOULD TAKE THIS.
WHAT IS IT?
THE LOCATION OF VEDA ITSELF
IS WRITTEN ON IT.
IT SHOWS THE LOCATION OF VEDA?
IF THE INNOVATORS FOUND OUT
ABOUT THIS,
THEY'D QUICKLY MOVE VEDA
TO SOME OTHER LOCATION.
YOU HAVE TO RECOVER VEDA
AS SOON AS YOU POSSIBLY CAN!
I UNDERSTAND.
COME ON, WE HAVE TO GET OUT
OF THIS PLACE, NOW.
NO, I'LL BE OKAY
RIGHT HERE.
BUT YOU CAN'T‐‐
ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW IS
I CANNOT GO WITH YOU.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME,
I'LL BE JUST FINE.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
(Sighs)
THE REASON I CAN'T GO
WITH YOU GUYS
IS BECAUSE MY GOAL
IS DIFFERENT FROM YOURS.
Saji:
SETSUNA!
SAJI, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
(Gasps)
WHAT THE...?!
THAT MACHINE.
IT'S BEEN FOUR YEARS,
YOUNG MAN.
NOW I REMEMBER HIM!
HMPH.
IT'S YOU AGAIN.
Graham:
YOUNG MAN, IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO LOSE YOUR GUNDAM,
YOU'LL GIVE ME
WHAT I DESIRE.
AND WHAT IS IT YOU WANT?
I WANT AN HONORABLE DUEL!
YOU WANT A WHAT?!
I, GRAHAM AKER,
STAND BEFORE YOU
AND HEREBY CHALLENGE YOU
TO A PROPER DUEL!
Regene:
MR. BUSHIDO.
DID RIBBONS PUT HIM UP TO THIS?
YOU'RE THAT DESPERATE TO
SETTLE THINGS BETWEEN US?
OF COURSE!
YOU HAVE SULLIED MY SKIES AND
STOLEN MY BROTHERS AND MENTOR!
EVEN THE PRIDE I FELT AS
A FLAG FIGHTER WAS SHATTERED
BECAUSE OF WHAT YOU DID!
YOU AND YOUR GUNDAM!
INDEED, THESE FEELINGS
HAVE SURPASSED LOVE,
TRANSCENDED HATRED.
THIS HAS BECOME DESTINY!
DESTINY?
DO YOU LAUGH AT MY OBSESSION?
DON'T FORGET
IT WAS THE GUNDAMS
WHO STARTED IT ALL WITH
THEIR ARMED INTERVENTIONS!
(Thinking)
HERE IS SOMEONE ELSE WHOSE LIFE
HAS BEEN TWISTED BY US.
VERY WELL.
I ACCEPT YOUR CHALLENGE.
HOLD NOTHING BACK!
SAJI!
GIVE ME CONTROL!
Saji:
YOU'RE GONNA FIGHT HIM?!
THERE'S NO WAY I CAN AVOID IT.
THIS IS THE PATH
I WISH TO TRAVEL UPON.
THE PATH OF BLOODSHED!
Setsuna:
DOUBLE 0 RAISER!
Graham:
THE REBORN MASURAO,
SUSANOWO!
ELIMINATING...
FINALLY, WE CROSS SWORDS...
...THE TARGET!
...IN EARNEST!
(Metal clashing)
Liu Mei:
I OFFER UP CELESTIAL BEING
AND THE INNOVATORS,
AND EVEN THE LIFE OF
MY DEAR OLDER BROTHER
TO REALIZE MY REFORMATION!
ALL FOR THE BRILLIANT FUTURE
THAT LIES BECKONING
AHEAD OF ME‐‐
Nena:
DON'T YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE NO FUTURE.
NENA!
BUT WHY?!
I ALREADY TOLD YOU.
I DESPISE YOU.
I ONLY OBEYED YOU BECAUSE
I HAD TO SURVIVE SOMEHOW.
I JUST HAD TO BE A LITTLE
FRIENDLY AND YOU BELIEVED ME.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOUR USEFULNESS IS OVER!
Nena:
(Laughing)
SHE'S BLOWN TO PIECES!
THAT'S YOUR PUNISHMENT
FOR TREATING ME
LIKE SOME KIND OF POSSESSION!
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES TO
SURVIVE IN THIS WORLD.
AND WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO BE HAPPY, AS WELL.
THAT'S THE REASON,
AND THAT'S WHY I'M OBEYING
THE INNOVATORS FOR NOW.
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T YET AVENGED
THE DEATHS OF MY BROTHERS!
AND WHEN THE TIME COMES
FOR MY VENGEANCE,
I'LL GO STRAIGHT FOR
THE JUGULAR!
(Ribbons' voice) DESPITE YOUR
WORDS, YOUR USEFULNESS IS OVER
AS WELL.
HARO?
THOSE WHO ACT SELFISHLY
MUST BE PUNISHED.
(Gasps)
AN INNOVATOR!
(Chuckles)
THE ONE TO PASS JUDGMENT ON YOU
WILL SOON BE ARRIVING.
THE ONE WHO'LL PASS JUDGMENT?!
(Gasps)
COULD IT BE...
HE'S THE ONE?
THAT'S JUST PERFECT!
I'LL HAVE VENGEANCE
FOR MY BROTHERS!
YES. I SUPPOSE YOU COULD
CALL IT VENGEANCE.
(Nena screaming)
WH‐WHAT?!
Louise:
THAT'S THE ONE!
THAT'S THE GUNDAM I WANT!
THE ONE THAT KILLED
MOM AND DAD!
THAT'S THE GUNDAM THAT DID IT!
Nena:
WHAT THE...?!
Setsuna:
THAT MACHINE! IT'S A THRONE!
(Gasps)
LOUISE'S FAMILY WAS‐‐
Setsuna:
LOUISE HALEVY, STOP IT!
LOUISE?!
REVENGE SOLVES NOTHING!
LOUISE!
Graham:
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU TO
HOLD NOTHING BACK!
(Setsuna and Saji screaming)
Nena:
TAKING REVENGE
FOR YOUR FAMILY?!
I'M DOING THE SAME THING!
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
SUFFERING HERE!
(Nena screaming)
(Thinking)
I WAS CREATED FOR THIS
AND FORCED TO FIGHT.
I REFUSE TO DIE LIKE THIS!
THIS ISN'T HOW I WANNA DIE!
(Gasps)
Louise:
I KNOW. I'M SURE
YOU DON'T WANNA DIE.
BUT, MY MOM AND DAD...
WEREN'T EVEN GIVEN THE CHANCE
TO SAY THAT
BEFORE YOU KILLED THEM!
(Screaming)
(Coughs)
DAMN YOU, YOU BITCH!
THE THRONE'S GONE!
LOUISE!
Graham:
KEEP YOUR MIND ON THE BATTLE!
MISTER BUSHIDO AND THE GUNDAM
ARE FIGHTING IN THAT DIRECTION.
WHERE'S THE WARRANT OFFICER?
OVER THERE!
Louise:
(Giggling)
I DID IT!
MOM, DAD.
I AVENGED YOU!
I DEFEATED THE GUNDAM!
WARRANT OFFICER.
(Hearty laughter)
LOOK, MOM!
LOOK, DAD!
SEE?
I FINALLY DID IT.
I DID IT, SO...
SAY SOMETHING.
TELL ME I'M GOOD!
TELL ME THAT I DID...
THE RIGHT THING.
(Sobbing)
(Louise screaming)
♪
Graham:
I SURVIVED FOR THIS!
THIS IS WHY I SURVIVED
UNTIL THIS DAY!
EVEN IF I SHOULD BE REDUCED TO
A PUPPET OF THE INNOVATORS!
THE WAY OF BUSHIDO!
(Metal clashing)
IS THIS WORTH IT?!
Saji:
SETSUNA!
I'M CONCENTRATING ON THE BATTLE!
Setsuna:
IF THIS KEEPS UP...
Graham:
WE'RE TOO EVENLY MATCHED!
IN THAT CASE...
THAT MEANS IT'S TIME!
Setsuna:
TRANS AM!
Graham:
(Aggressive yell)
(Yelling)
IT'S TIME FOR THE AWAKENING.
(Gasps)
WHERE THE HELL AM I?
COULD IT BE THAT I'VE ALREADY
MADE THE PASSAGE TO NIRVANA?
Setsuna:
NO.
YOUNG MAN.
I BELIEVE THIS IS THE PLACE
WHERE THE QUANTA
CONVERGE TOGETHER.
WHAT KIND OF NONSENSE IS THIS?
Setsuna:
I FEEL THAT I UNDERSTAND
WHY AEOLIA SCHENBERG CREATED
THE GUNDAMS.
OR RATHER,
WHY HE CREATED THE GN DRIVES.
WHAT?!
THE ARMED INTERVENTIONS
WERE TO PREPARE FOR THIS.
AEOLIA'S GOAL
WAS TO GUIDE HUMANITY TO
REFORMATION.
AND SO,
I'M READY.
I'M GOING TO REFORM MYSELF.
Narrator:
TO RECOVER VEDA,
AN OPERATION TO FORCE THEIR WAY
THROUGH THE A‐LAWS FLEET
GETS UNDERWAY.
NEXT EPISODE:
"FOR THE FUTURE".
EVEN IF THIS BATTLE
BURDENS THEM WITH SIN,
IT IS WORTH IT
IF IT LEADS TO TOMORROW.