WH‐WHAT IS THIS?
Andrei:
THAT MACHINE!
Setsuna:
A VOICE?
Bring:
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I CAN HEAR VOICES.
THE VOICES
OF EVERYONE HERE.
Louise:
GUNDAM!
THAT VOICE!
IT COULDN'T BE... LOUISE?
LOUISE!
WHAT? WHY AM I HEARING
SAJI'S VOICE?
Saji:
LOUISE, DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE IN A MOBILE SUIT.
WHERE ARE YOU?!
SAJI! WHERE?
ARE YOU...IN THAT GUNDAM?
LOUISE, YOU'RE NOT WITH
THE A‐LAWS, ARE YOU?
SAJI, CAN I ASK YOU TO
REALIZE MY DREAM FOR ME?
Louise: (Flashback)
SAJI, WHY?!
MY DREAM IS SIMPLE...
BUT WHY ARE YOU‐‐
IT'S TO MAKE
YOUR DREAM COME TRUE.
WHY?!
TO GO INTO SPACE.
(Flashback)
WELL, WHY ARE YOU?
SO, PLEASE, I NEED YOU TO HELP
ME FULFILL MY DREAM.
Both:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?!
Louise:
THEN IT'S A PROMISE.
♪
(Lasers blast)
(Grunts)
(Boom)
(Groans)
(Grunts)
(Blast)
SAJI!
LOUISE!
YOU WILL NOT
PASS ME!
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
(Tensed grunt)
(Struggling grunts)
(Lasers blast)
DAMN IT! WHAT?!
(Boom)
(Bracing grunt)
(Loud explosion)
(Surprised gasp)
WHAT'S THIS?
(Lasers blast)
MORE REINFORCEMENTS?
I CAN'T RISK USING TRANS AM
IN THIS SITUATION!
BEHIND YOU! BEHIND YOU!
WHAT IS?!
(Lyle groans)
FOR MY COLONEL
AND HER VICTORY!
NOW'S THE TIME!
(Worried sigh)
CHERUDIM IS...
Patrick:
WHAT THE‐‐
WHAT WAS THAT?
IS THAT...?
SO THEY DID DOCK.
THE DOUBLE 0 RAISER!
Revive:
COMPRESSED PARTICLE
RECHARGE COMPLETE.
A VOICE.
(Scoffs)
THIS WILL FINISH IT!
Setsuna:
A NEW MODEL?
A VOICE?!
THERE IT IS!
NOT YET!
MADNESS! NEVERTHELESS,
I AM... AN INNOVATOR!
(Setsuna gasps)
TH‐THAT CAN'T BE!
WHAT THE‐‐
Revive:
RIGHT THERE!
(Boom)
DON'T MOCK ME!
(Yelling)
(Boom)
DEFEATED. I'M AN INNOVATOR
AND I WAS DEFEATED.
(Alert buzzes)
(Panting)
THE TIME LIMIT'S UP.
BUT WHAT JUST HAPPENED
BACK THERE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
PTOLEMY NEEDS US.
Saji:
I HAVE TO GO.
I HAVE TO GO...
TO LOUISE.
WHEREVER SHE IS.
TO LOUISE!
THE SUIT QUANTIZED?
A GUNDAM POWER THAT EVEN
I WASN'T AWARE OF?
HUH?
OH, IS SOMETHING
THE MATTER?
YOU SEEM RATHER
UNSETTLED BY WHAT HAPPENED.
(Yelps)
SHUT UP.
YOU GREEDY BITCH.
(Trembling breath)
DAMN! HOW ARE WE GOING TO WIN
WITHOUT THE GADESSA?
WITHDRAWAL ORDERS?
Feldt:
ENEMY MOBILE SUITS
HAVE BEGUN FALLING BACK.
PTOLEMY CEASE FIRING.
GUNDAMS,
ASSUME DEFENSIVE POSITIONS.
Tiera:
ROGER.
HOW MANY MACHINES DID
SETSUNA TAKE OUT?
I THINK IT WAS
ALMOST TEN OF THEM.
DON'T RELAX JUST YET.
OUR MAIN OBJECTIVE
IS STILL
THE DESTRUCTION
OF THE SATELLITE WEAPON.
MILEINA, I REALIZE YOU MUST BE
WORRIED ABOUT YOUR PARENTS,
BUT I NEED YOU
TO USE THE KARELS
TO REPAIR PTOLEMY AND
THE GUNDAMS.
ROGER THAT, MA'AM.
THIS IS ARIOS,
I'VE ESCORTED ALL THE
TRANSPORTS TO A SAFE DISTANCE.
AND MILEINA,
YOUR MOM'S OKAY TOO.
(Pleased gasp)
ISN'T THAT GREAT NEWS,
MILEINA?
IT SURE IS!
I'LL GO TAKE CARE OF
THE REPAIRS, NOW!
(Sighs)
DOUBLE 0 RAISER.
WHO WOULD'VE IMAGINED SUCH
INCREDIBLE ABILITIES?
(Frustrated grunts)
Saji:
MOVE! COME ON, MOVE!
SAJI CROSSROAD.
COME ON, MOVE,
DAMN IT!
(Panting)
I HAVE TO GO
TO WHERE LOUISE IS.
(Crying)
I HEARD... SAJI'S VOICE.
SAJI WAS THERE.
HE WAS WITH CELESTIAL BEING.
WORKING TOGETHER WITH
THE BASTARDS
WHO KILLED MOM AND DAD.
(Gasps)
SETSUNA. HE WAS A MEMBER
OF THAT GROUP, TOO.
AND SAJI LIVED
NEXT DOOR TO HIM.
THAT MEANS
THEY WERE CONNECTED
ALL ALONG.
(Pained gasp)
(Struggling to breath)
(Gulps)
THE DOUBLE POWERED GUNDAM'S
PERFORMANCE WAS SO EXCEPTIONAL.
JUST WHAT IS THAT MACHINE?
ANEW, WHAT'S IAN'S CONDITION?
HIS INJURIES AREN'T
LIFE‐THREATENING.
HE SHOULD BE FULLY RECOVERED
WITHIN TEN DAYS.
HUH?
SAJI CROSSROAD.
I HEARD LOUISE'S VOICE.
SHE WAS PILOTING
A MOBILE SUIT.
SHE CALLED OUT... MY NAME.
BUT WHY IS
SHE WITH THE A‐LAWS?
(Chuckles)
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
SHE DESPISES THE GUNDAMS!
LOUISE'S PARENTS WERE KILLED BY
GUNDAMS RIGHT IN FRONT OF HER!
IT'S ALL BECAUSE
OF YOU GUYS.
IT'S YOUR FAULT
LOUISE JOINED THE A‐LAWS.
AND THEN SHE...
WHY? WHY DID THIS HAPPEN?
WHY DID IT HAVE TO
BE LIKE THIS?
Setsuna:
WHY DID IT
HAVE TO BE LIKE THIS?
YEAH, I ALWAYS WONDERED
THE SAME THING.
TO RESIST FATE,
YOU HAVE TO...
FIGHT.
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO
GET LOUISE HALEVY
BACK FROM THE A‐LAWS,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO FIGHT.
I SHOULD...FIGHT THEM?
IF SHE'S THAT
IMPORTANT TO YOU,
THEN YOU SHOULD
BE ABLE TO.
YOU'RE SAYING YOU WANT ME
TO KILL PEOPLE?!
NO, I'M NOT.
YOU'LL JUST BE FIGHTING
TO BRING HER BACK.
YOU'RE JUST MINCING WORDS!
WHEN YOU FIGHT,
PEOPLE GET HURT!
LIKE LOUISE.
WHEN YOU FIGHT,
DO IT FOR YOUR OWN SAKE.
(Pained grunt)
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
LISTEN, I'M NOT LIKE
THE REST OF YOU!
DON'T THINK THAT I AM!
(Fuming grunt)
EAVESDROPPING AGAIN?
IT WASN'T MY FAULT
I OVERHEARD.
BUT YOU KNOW,
YOU REALLY MESSED THAT UP.
WHAT?
IT PROBABLY WOULD
HAVE BEEN BEST
IF YOU'D BEEN A LITTLE
CLEARER WITH THE KID.
YOU SHOULD HAVE SAID,
"I'LL DO THE FIGHTING.
"YOU JUST FOCUS
ON CHANGING HER MIND
"OR WHATEVER YOU'VE
GOT TO DO
"TO GET HER
TO LEAVE THE A‐LAWS."
THERE'S NO GUARANTEE
SHE'LL COME BACK.
SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE
PRETTY EAGER TO HELP.
MAKING UP FOR MISTAKES
IN THE PAST?
NOT IN THE PAST.
THIS IS FOR THE FUTURE.
(Sobbing)
(Rip)
Huh?
THAT PHOTO, SIR,
IS SHE YOUR WIFE?
Zinin:
UNTIL TWO MONTHS AGO,
THAT IS.
SHE WAS KILLED IN
ONE OF KATHRON'S ACTS
OF ANTI‐FEDERATION TERRORISM.
(Emotional sigh)
(Tensed breath)
(Door slides open)
I THOUGHT I'D FIND YOU HERE,
WARRANT OFFICER.
(Gasps)
I HEARD CAPTAIN ZININ WAS
PROMOTED TO LIEUTENANT COLONEL.
OH, IS THAT SO.
WHEN WE WERE FIGHTING, I HEARD
A VOICE, WARRANT OFFICER.
TELL ME,
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU WERE COMMUNICATING WITH
THE ENEMY, WEREN'T YOU?
NO, I WASN'T.
BUT WARRANT OFFICER,
YOU DO KNOW ONE
OF THE ENEMY.
HE SEEMED LIKE
A CLOSE FRIEND OF YOURS.
HE'S NOT! THOSE PEOPLE
KILLED MY FAMILY!
THEY'LL BRING NOTHING
BUT CHAOS TO OUR WORLD!
AND THAT'S WHY I‐‐
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SUCH A SLENDER ARM.
YOU WOULDN'T THINK
IT BELONGED TO A PILOT.
SOMEONE LIKE YOU SHOULDN'T
BE IN THE A‐LAWS.
(Winces)
EXCUSE ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE WERE BESTED
IN BATTLE BY MERE HUMANS!
IF ONLY RIBBONS HAD TOLD US
WHAT THE TWIN DRIVE WAS REALLY
CAPABLE OF DOING!
RIBBONS ALMARK?
BRING, DID YOU HEAR THAT?
WE'RE TO CAPTURE THE DOUBLE 0.
AND HE'S GETTING
HILING AND DIVINE
INVOLVED IN THIS AS WELL.
IS IT...IS IT POSSIBLE THAT
NOT EVEN RIBBONS
KNEW ABOUT THE
TWIN DRIVE'S CAPABILITIES?
OH! WHAT'S THAT?
WHAT?
(Rumbling)
Subordinate:
THE SATELLITE WEAPON
WAS FIRED AGAIN?
YEAH, AT RICHIELA'S
MILITARY BASE.
ARE ALL THE MIDDLE EASTERN
ARMIES BEING WIPED OUT?
HOLD ON A MINUTE.
WASN'T THERE A REFUGEE CAMP
WITH OVER A MILLION PEOPLE
NEXT TO RICHIELA'S BASE?
THEY MIGHT HAVE
BEEN WIPED OUT TOO.
JUST KILLING
INNOCENT PEOPLE LIKE THAT.
TO HELL WITH THEIR
SO‐CALLED UNITED WORLD!
(Angry grunt)
Klaus:
DOES THE FEDERATION
GOVERNMENT REALLY BELIEVE
THESE KINDS OF METHODS
WILL BRING
ABOUT A LASTING PEACE?!
(Heavy breathing)
(Footsteps)
(Peaceful moan)
IT SEEMS AS IF ALL OUR LANDS,
OUR PEOPLE,
OUR COUNTRIES ARE DISAPPEARING.
UNDER A GAG ORDER?
JUST WHAT ARE YOU SAYING,
COMMANDER?
IT'S OBVIOUS THAT THE A‐LAWS
USED THE SOLAR POWER
GENERATION SYSTEM
TO PERFORM A HIGH‐OUTPUT LASER
ATTACK FROM ORBIT!
A WEAPON OF MASS
DESTRUCTION LIKE THAT IS‐‐
THIS IS AN ORDER FROM
THE FEDERATION PRESIDENT.
WE CAN'T IGNORE IT.
ALL OF THE SOLDIERS
OUT HERE
WITNESSED THE
DESTRUCTION FIRSTHAND!
RUMORS ARE GOING TO
SPREAD QUICKLY.
MANY OF THEM ARE
STARTING TO QUESTION
THE METHODS OF THE A‐LAWS!
THAT'S WHY I WANT
YOU TO ACT AS A MONITOR
TO MAKE SURE THE GAG ORDER
IS STRICTLY ENFORCED.
IS THAT A DIRECT ORDER,
COMMANDER?
OF COURSE IT IS.
AND THERE WILL BE NO CHANGE
IN MILITARY POLICY.
(Sighs)
A SOLDIER ALWAYS FOLLOWS ORDERS.
FELDT,
HAS THERE BEEN ANY RESPONSE AT
ALL FROM WANG LIU MEI?
NO, SHE HASN'T
REPLIED YET.
WE NEED RELIABLE INFORMATION ON
THE SATELLITE WEAPON.
HMM?
I'M GETTING
A REPORT THE SATELLITE WEAPON
HAS FIRED A SECOND SHOT
AT EARTH!
WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
WE CAN'T WASTE ANY
MORE TIME!
ATTENTION ALL HANDS,
THIS IS SUMERAGI!
AS SOON AS THE REPAIRS TO
PTOLEMY'S HULL ARE COMPLETE,
WE'LL USE TRANS AM TO MOVE OUT
AT FULL ACCELERATION.
WE'LL BEGIN OUR ASSAULT
ON THE ENEMY SATELLITE WEAPON
ON THE ORBITAL RING!
REPAIRS ON THE GUNDAMS WILL
CONTINUE AS WE ACCELERATE.
EVERYONE, LET'S GIVE IT
OUR BEST.
BUT, LOUISE IS IN
THIS SECTOR.
I'LL BE LEAVING HER.
I NEED A FAVOR, HARO.
WHAT IS IT?
MILEINA.
MR. ERDE.
IT'LL DEFINITELY BE
FIXED FOR THE MISSION.
MAKE SURE.
I WONDER IF KLAUS
AND MY FRIENDS ARE SAFE?
(Grunts)
HUH?
MR. CROSSROAD?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
UM, JUST A LITTLE SOMETHING
THEY ASKED ME TO DO.
BYE!
HE SEEMS KIND OF...
I HAVE TO SEE LOUISE!
SHE SHOULDN'T
BE WITH THE A‐LAWS.
THIS HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH US.
WE SHOULDN'T EVEN BE HERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE!
JUST LEAVE WAR TO THE GUYS
WHO ACTUALLY WANT TO FIGHT!
WE'RE GOING TO
GET BACK EVERYTHING WE HAD.
THOSE TIMES, THOSE DAYS.
HUH?
Tiera: (Flashback)
IGNORING REALITY LIKE THAT
IS JUST A KIND
OF INADVERTENT MALICE.
AND THEN THINGS LIKE
THIS HAPPEN!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
TOOK THEIR LIVES, YOU KNOW!
THROUGH YOUR
OWN FOOLISH ACTIONS!
(Stunned gasps)
I WAS ABOUT TO DO
THE SAME THING.
BUT WHAT SHOULD I DO?
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
OH, LOUISE.
THE SOLAR REACTORS OF CHERUDIM,
ARIOS, AND SERAVEE
ARE NOW DIRECTLY LINKED UP TO
PTOLEMY'S POWER SYSTEM.
INITIATE TRANS AM!
TRANS AM!
Sumeragi:
PTOLEMY, MAXIMUM OUTPUT!
Anew:
ROGER!
(Crying)
I'M SORRY, LOUISE.
Saji:
LOUISE.
♪
Subordinate:
IN TEN MINUTES, OUR SPACE
FLEETS WILL REACH THE POINT
WHERE THEY'RE
WITHIN STRIKING DISTANCE
OF THE SATELLITE WEAPON.
THIS BATTLE WILL
DETERMINE EVERYTHING.
HMM?
Klaus:
WE MUST HAVE FAITH...
IN OUR COMRADES.
Operator:
WE HAVE VISUAL ON
THE SATELLITE WEAPON.
WHAT'S THE CURRENT STATUS
OF THE SECOND FLEET?
IT'S APPROACHING
ITS DESIGNATED POINT NOW, SIR.
VERY GOOD. AS SOON
AS IT REACHES POSITION,
THE TWO FLEETS WILL
BEGIN CONDUCTING
STAGGERED MISSILE ATTACKS
ON THE TARGET.
CAPTAIN.
THE SATELLITE WEAPON
IS MOVING!
IT'S MOVING?
Operator:
THE LASER BARREL
IS EMERGING FROM THE TOP!
THAT ANGLE HAS IT POINTED
AT THE SECOND FLEET.
(Blast)
HALF THE SECOND FLEET WAS
JUST WIPED OUT, SIR!
(Growling)
A THIRD SHOT WAS JUST
FIRED INTO SPACE.
FELDT! ANALYZE IT!
R‐ROGER!
THAT WEAPON, CAN FIRE
INTO SPACE, TOO?
WHAT WAS IT
AIMING AT?
IT WAS AIMED AT
KATHARON'S SPACE FLEET.
AT WHAT?!
DAMN THOSE BASTARDS.
THESE ARE THE FEDERATION'S...
NO, THESE ARE
THE INNOVATOR'S METHODS.
Narrator:
IN ORDER TO DESTROY THE
SATELLITE WEAPON,
CELESTIAL BEING UNDERTAKES
A DEATH‐DEFYING MISSION.
NEXT EPISODE:
"ASSAULT ON MEMENTO MORI".
THIS IS THE TRUE SPIRIT
OF A GUNDAM MEISTER.