Haro:
GN DRIVE LINKAGE COMPLETE!
CONNECTION CONFIRMED.
ALL 00 COMPONENTS READING
SATISFACTORY.
THE TWO SOLAR REACTORS ARE
WITHIN NORMAL PARAMETERS.
ALRIGHT.
LET'S BEGIN THE MATCHING TEST.
YOU CAN GO AHEAD, TIERIA.
ROGER THAT.
GN DRIVE,
DISENGAGING REPAUSE.
Feldt:
TOPOLOGICAL DEFECT CHANGING
FROM GROUND STATE
TO HIGH OUTPUT.
TWIN DRIVE'S PARTICLE
SYNCHRONIZATION RATE IS AT 35%,
37, 40,
47, 49, 55, 58.
WE'VE JUST BROKEN
THE 60% BARRIER.
IF IT MAKES IT PAST 80%,
WE'LL BE WITHIN
STABLE OPERATIONAL RANGE.
IT'S LOOKING GOOD.
WE'VE DEVELOPED AN INSTABILITY
IN THE TOPOLOGICAL DEFECT!
SAY WHAT?!
TWIN DRIVE SYNC RATE
DECREASING,
FUSION RATE IS ALSO FALLING!
WELL THAT'S IT.
WE'VE NOW TESTED
EVERY POSSIBLE COMBINATION
WITH OUR PRESENT RESOURCES.
WHY WON'T IT WORK?!
WHY WON'T IT STABILIZE?!
WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE WE MISSING?!
THE ONLY OPTION LEFT IS
EXIA'S SOLAR REACTOR.
NO MATTER WHAT, WE'VE GOTTA
GET THIS THING WORKING
BEFORE THOSE GUYS
GO INTO ACTION.
SO THAT'S OUR LAST HOPE.
EXIA'S GN DRIVE.
♪
(Bell ringing)
WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH YOU?
YOU CALL ME HERE AND THEN
JUST FLAT OUT TELL ME
YOU'RE FROM
CELESTIAL BEING.
NEIL DYLANDY...
WAS A GUNDAM MEISTER.
MY BROTHER WAS
A GUNDAM MEISTER?
THAT'S RIGHT.
HE PILOTED A GUNDAM.
HE "PILOTED"?
WAIT A MINUTE.
HE'S NOT DEAD, IS HE?
IN BATTLE, FOUR YEARS AGO.
YOU'RE TELLING ME
I SHOULD CARRY OUT HIS WILL
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
I'M NOT SAYING THAT AT ALL.
BUT IF YOU TRULY
WANT TO CHANGE THIS WORLD,
JUST AS NEIL DYLANDY
ALWAYS WANTED TO,
AND,
IF YOU'RE WILLING
TO FIGHT FOR THAT...
YOU'LL FIND
ALL THE INFORMATION
YOU NEED TO KNOW ABOUT US
IN HERE.
ARE YOU SURE?
WHAT IF I TURN THIS OVER
TO THE AUTHORITIES?
THE SECURITY AGENCY
IS ABOUT TO MOVE AGAINST
KATHARON IN EUROPE.
THEY'RE GOING TO ATTACK
THEIR BASES.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
THOSE GUYS ARE SERIOUS.
COLONEL KATI MANNEQUIN,
HEREBY ACCEPTING
MY NEW POSITION.
I'M PLEASED TO MAKE
YOUR ACQUINTANCE, COLONEL.
SIR.
AS YOU'RE AWARE,
COLONEL,
OUR AUTONOMOUS PEACEKEEPING
FORCE KNOWN AS THE A‐LAWS
WAS ESTABLISHED TO SUPPRESS
ANTI‐FEDERATION ELEMENTS
AND REPORTS DIRECTLY TO
THE FEDERATION GOVERNMENT.
OUR OFFENSIVE TARGETS INCLUDE
ANY NON‐FEDERATION NATIONS THAT
HAVE RETAINED THEIR MILITARY
AND THE ANTI‐GOVERNMENT
ORGANIZATION KNOWN AS KATHARON.
AND NOW,
IT SEEMS ONE MORE
VERY IMPORTANT TARGET
HAS BEEN ADDED
TO THAT LIST.
THE GUNDAMS, I PRESUME.
IF THEY INTEND TO
START PERFORMING
THEIR ARMED INTERVENTIONS AGAIN,
THEN OUR FORCES WILL HAVE
NO CHOICE BUT TO RETALIATE.
PUBLIC OPINION WOULD SUPPORT
ANY ACTION WE MIGHT TAKE.
IT'S IMPORTANT YOU KNOW
HOW MUCH I VALUE
YOUR ABILITIES AND SKILLS,
GIVEN THE FACT YOU HAVE
ACTUAL COMBAT EXPERIENCE
BATTLING THE GUNDAMS.
THE A‐LAWS WILL GIVE YOU
THE CHANCE TO USE THOSE SKILLS.
YES, SIR!
(Thinking)
THE AUTONOMOUS
PEACEKEEPING FORCE, A‐LAWS.
FAITHFUL WATCHDOG
OF THE FEDERATION.
PERMISSION TO SPEAK WITH YOU,
COLONEL?
HMM?
LIEUTENANT PERIES?
SO YOU'RE WITH THE A‐LAWS, TOO?
YES, MA'AM.
THEY CAME CALLING FOR ME,
AND I ACCEPTED
THE POSITION YESTERDAY.
I'M SURPRISED COLONEL SMIRNOV
GAVE HIS PERMISSION FOR THIS.
AN ORDER FROM THE TOP
HAS TO BE OBEYED.
AND WHO ARE YOU?
I'M ANDREI SMIRNOV, MA'AM.
I CARRY THE RANK OF LIEUTENANT.
LIEUTENANT SMIRNOV?
ARE YOU BY ANY CHANCE
COLONEL SMIRNOV'S‐‐
Andrei:
YES, MA'AM. I'M HIS SON.
SO THEY'VE ADDED THE MISSION
COMMANDER FROM THE AEU
AND THE SUPER SOLDIER
FROM THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE.
THAT'S COMMANDER KATAGIRI
FOR YOU.
HE DOESN'T WASTE TIME.
Ian:
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL DO A MATCHING TEST
WITH EXIA'S SOLAR REACTOR
ON OUR WAY BACK TO THE BASE.
THE SIMULATION SHOWED
THE LINKAGE RATIO
BETWEEN EXIA'S
AND THE 0 GUNDAM'S
SOLAR REACTORS TO BE HIGH.
YEAH, BUT WE WON'T REALLY KNOW
UNTIL WE TRY IT OUT.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM
WITH THE NEW
GUNDAM MAIN ENGINE THEORY
AEOLIA SCHENBERG SENT US
ALONG WITH THE TRANS‐AM.
IS IT JUST AN ABSTRACT THEORY,
OR AN ACCURATE PREDICTION
OF SCIENCE
200 YEARS IN THE FUTURE?
BY SYNCHRONIZING
TWO SOLAR REACTORS,
THE RESULTING PARTICLE EMISSIONS
ARE SQUARED.
THAT'S THE 00'S
TWIN DRIVE SYSTEM.
(Cheerfully)
HI, WE'VE BROUGHT YOU
SOMETHING TO EAT!
I'LL LEAVE IT RIGHT HERE,
SO JUST HELP YOURSELF!
AND WE'LL BE LEAVING RED HARO
HERE TO KEEP YOU COMPANY!
PLEASED TO MEET YOU!
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING FROM ME,
OR THE OTHERS,
JUST TELL IT TO RED HARO.
YOU'LL ALSO BE ABLE TO
ACCESS OUR DATABASE.
HOW MUCH LONGER
ARE YOU GONNA KEEP ME HERE?
HUH?
LISTEN, WE KNOW THE A‐LAWS
ARE LOOKING FOR YOU.
LOOK, I'M NOT
A MEMBER OF KATHARON!
WELL, LET'S HOPE THAT THEY THINK
YOU'RE NOT A MEMBER EITHER.
ARE YOU PEOPLE STILL
PLANNING ON PERFORMING
THOSE ARMED INTERVENTIONS
LIKE YOU DID BEFORE?
Lasse:
NO. WE'RE GONNA
TAKE ON THE A‐LAWS.
THE FEDERATION FORCES?
IT'S AN AUTONOMOUS FORCE
THAT REPORTS TO THE GOVERNMENT.
THEY'VE ALREADY COMMITTED
14 ACTS OF MASS MURDER,
ATROCITIES
THEY CALL SUPPRESSION.
THEY'VE PRODUCED
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF CASUALTIES,
THOUGH ALL RECORDS OF
THESE ATTACKS
HAVE BEEN ERASED.
I BELIEVE YOU'VE EXPERIENCED
THEIR METHODS FIRST HAND.
BUT WHAT DOES IT ALL MEAN?!
WASN'T THE FEDERATION GOVERNMENT
FORMED IN THE FIRST PLACE
BECAUSE OF
YOUR INTERVENTIONS?
THAT'S WHY WE INTEND
TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT AGAIN.
BUT IF YOU FIGHT,
MORE INNOCENT PEOPLE
WILL BE HURT!
WHETHER WE FIGHT OR NOT,
PEOPLE ARE GONNA DIE.
(Frustrated grunt)
MR. AEON, THE TEST IS GOING
TO BE STARTING ANY MINUTE NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
AND HIM?
WHAT'S SETSUNA DOING
RIGHT NOW?
OH, HE'S GONE TO
PICK UP SOME PEOPLE!
HE'S TRACKING DOWN
A FEW OF OUR COMRADES.
(Sighs)
COME ON.
THAT'S ENOUGH NOW,
KNOCK IT OFF.
(Disappointed sigh)
YOU'RE DRINKING
WAY TOO MUCH.
HONESTLY, I CAN'T KEEP
LOOKING AFTER YOU.
I'M LEAVING THEN.
WHAT?
GOODBYE, BILLY.
THANKS FOR THE LAST TWO YEARS.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
WHOA, WHOA,
WAIT A MINUTE, KUJO.
I REALLY DIDN'T MEAN IT
TO COME OUT THAT WAY.
(Doorbell rings)
LOOKS LIKE
WE HAVE A VISITOR.
(Surprised gasp)
SOMEONE YOU KNOW?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU ACTUALLY
TOLD ONE OF YOUR OLD FRIENDS
WHERE YOU'RE LIVING
RIGHT NOW!
IT'S PERFECT!
WHY DON'T WE ASK HIM TO COME
HAVE LUNCH WITH US?
NO, WAIT!
Billy:
IT WOULD BE KINDA NICE
TO REMINISCE
ABOUT THE PAST WITH A FRIEND.
(Gasps)
SETSUNA.
IT IS YOU.
IT'S BEEN FOUR YEARS,
MISS SUMERAGI.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
THAT ISN'T HER NAME.
THE PERSON
YOU'RE TALKING TO IS‐‐
HER CODENAME IS
SUMERAGI LEE NORIEGA.
SHE'S CELESTIAL BEING'S
TACTICAL FORECASTER.
(Shocked gasp)
NOW, YOU DON'T HAVE
ANYWHERE YOU CAN RUN.
Lyle:
YOU WERE ACTUALLY RAIDED
BY THE SECURITY AGENCY?
SO, ANY CASUALTIES?
I SEE.
RIGHT, I'LL CALL YOU
BACK SOON.
(Phone beeping)
Lyle:
THIS IS JEAN ONE.
PLEASE GET BACK TO ME
IMMEDIATELY. IT'S IMPORTANT,
SO I THINK WE SHOULD MEET
FACE TO FACE.
Ian:
THE EXIA AND 0 GUNDAM MATCH UP
HAS YIELDED THE HIGHEST
SYNC NUMBERS SO FAR,
BUT IT STILL HASN'T GONE
ABOVE 70%.
WE'RE ONLY 10% AWAY
FROM STABLE TERRITORY.
WE COULD TRY FORCING
ACTIVATION WITH TRANS‐AM.
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
IF WE DO THAT,
IT COULD OVERLOAD,
OR MAYBE EVEN BLOW ITSELF UP!
THEN ALL WE CAN DO IS
RECALIBRATE
AND CHECK
THE WHOLE SYSTEM AGAIN.
(Frustrated growl)
OF COURSE WE WILL!
IT WAS DETERMINED
THAT THE GUNDAM THRONES
WERE RESPONSIBLE FOR
THE ATTACK ON CIVILIANS
THAT TOOK PLACE IN SPAIN.
THE REASON FOR THAT ATTACK,
UNKNOWN.
GUNDAM THRONES?
THE THRONE MACHINES WERE NOT
PART OF THE ORIGINAL PLAN.
ALSO, THE THRONES ARE EQUIPPED
WITH PSEUDO GN DRIVES.
THE OFFENSIVE PARTICLES
THEY EMIT
MAY POSSIBLY AFFECT
THE HUMAN BODY.
AFFECT THE HUMAN BODY?
Saji:
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?!
WHY WON'T THE REGENERATION
TREATMENT WORK ON HER HAND?
Nurse:
THE DOCTOR THINKS
THERE MUST HAVE BEEN SOMETHING
ABOUT THE GUNDAM'S BEAM WEAPON
THAT CAUSED
THESE CELLULAR DEFECTS.
GUNDAM THRONES.
THESE ARE THE MACHINES
THAT HURT LOUISE!
THEY'RE ENEMIES!
HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'LL ACCOMPLISH
BY DRAGGING ME BACK IN?
EVEN WITH
THE FEDERATION GOVERNMENT
THE WORLD HASN'T CHANGED
ONE BIT.
EVEN WITH ALL THOSE SACRIFICES
NOTHING HAS CHANGED.
AEOLIA'S PLAN
WAS MEANINGLESS.
IS THAT WHY YOU'VE BEEN DRUNK
ALL THIS TIME?
IS THAT A PROBLEM?
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS.
I CAN'T GO ON ANYMORE.
YEAH, BUT I,
I MEAN, WE ARE GONNA FIGHT.
Setsuna:
IF LEADING THE WORLD
INTO A TERRIBLE REFORMATION
IS OUR SIN,
THEN THE ONLY WAY
WE CAN MAKE UP FOR THAT SIN
IS TO CHANGE THE WORLD AGAIN.
I'M AFRAID
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE FOR ME.
YOU'RE RUNNING AWAY?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
JUST LET ME DISAPPEAR.
I DON'T HAVE THE KIND OF
INNER STRENGTH THAT YOU HAVE.
Announcer:
EXPRESS F‐120 LEAVING
GEOSTATIONARY ORBITAL STATION
FOR GRAND UNION‐‐
PLEASE, SETSUNA.
JUST FORGET ABOUT ME.
HERE COMES
THE NEW MEISTER NOW.
SO THERE'S A NEW MEISTER.
HUH?
YO! YOU GUYS ARE
RUNNING A LITTLE LATE!
IS THAT LOCKON?!
IS HE REALLY...IS HE ALIVE?!
GET OUT OF HERE, DO I REALLY
LOOK LIKE MY BROTHER THAT MUCH?
YOU'RE...
YOU'RE HIS BROTHER?
LET ME INTRODUCE YOU.
THIS IS LYLE DYLANDY‐‐
NO, YOU'RE WRONG.
MY NAME IS LOCKON STRATOS.
I'M A GUNDAM MEISTER FOR
CELESTIAL BEING.
Shirin:
KLAUS. JEAN ONE
HAS MADE CONTACT
WITH CELESTIAL BEING.
NOW, THE QUESTION IS WHETHER OR
NOT THEY'LL COOPERATE WITH US.
THE WAY
THE FEDERATION GOVERNMENT
IS USING ACCESS TO
THE SOLAR POWER SYSTEM
TO COERCE ITS MEMBER NATIONS
WHILE ABANDONING
THE NON‐MEMBER NATIONS
IS SIMPLY UNJUST.
NOT ONLY THAT,
BUT IN ITS RUSH TO UNIFY,
THE FEDERATION ESTABLISHED
ITS OWN AUTONOMOUS
PEACEKEEPING FORCE
TO SUPPRESS
ANYONE WHO DARED OPPOSE IT.
AT THIS RATE, THE FEDERATION
WILL BECOME A DICTATORSHIP.
AND I'M SURE THOSE GUYS KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
I CERTAINLY HOPE SO.
TO THINK THE GUNDAMS
HAVE APPEARED AGAIN.
ARE YOU A PART OF THIS,
SETSUNA?
(Gasps)
MARINA ISMAIL,
RIGHT?
YOU'RE COMING WITH US.
(Scared gasp)
Hong‐Long:
MISTRESS.
WHY DID YOU GIVE THEM
THAT INFORMATION
ABOUT CELESTIAL BEING?
WHAT HAVE WE SPENT
THESE LAST
FOUR YEARS PREPARING FOR?!
THEY'RE OF NO USE TO ANYONE
IF THEY CAN'T OVERCOME
THIS LEVEL OF DANGER.
MISTRESS.
TO MY EYES
IT APPEARS THAT
YOU'RE MORE INTERESTED IN
STARTING FIGHTS
THAN IN
REFORMING THE WORLD.
I AM.
Liu‐Mei:
IT'S ONLY WHEN THE BATTLES
ARE OVER
THAT TRUE REFORM
FOR THE WORLD WILL BE FOUND.
YOU CAN MAKE CONTACT
WITH THEM NOW.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT,
MY MISTRESS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
RIBBONS?
Regene:
WOW, FANTASTIC INFORMATION!
WELL, WHAT ELSE
WOULD YOU EXPECT
FROM A FORMER
CELESTIAL BEING AGENT.
SHOULD WE CONTACT
HOMER KATAGIRI?
YES, GOOD THINKING.
MY THOUGHTS EXACTLY.
WE KNOW THE LOCATION OF
THE SPACESHIP
THAT'S CARRYING THE GUNDAMS?
IT'S COMING STRAIGHT
FROM HEADQUARTERS.
I'D SAY IT'S RELIABLE, SIR.
COMMANDER KATAGIRI
DOES IT AGAIN.
HE PLAYS HIS CARDS WELL.
PREPARE TO LAUNCH
ALL MOBILE SUIT TEAMS!
THIS SHIP IS GOING TO CONDUCT
A SURPRISE ATTACK
ON THE GUNDAMS' SPACESHIP!
AHEAD TEAMS ONE AND TWO,
PREPARE TO SORTIE!
Louise:
CAPTAIN! PLEASE GIVE ME
PERMISSION TO SORTIE!
I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO MAKES THAT DECISION!
REMAIN ON STANDBY,
WARRANT OFFICER HALEVY.
Mechanic:
YOUR SUSPENSION SETTINGS
ARE ALL GOOD, SIR!
Zinin:
NICE WORK.
STARTUP AHEAD!
ALL UNITS, HURRY UP WITH
YOUR LAUNCH PREP!
DAMN CELESTIAL BEING.
I'M READY! LAUNCHING AHEAD!
EMERGENCY TRANSMISSION,
IT'S COMING FROM PTOLEMY.
Lasse:
I HAVE SOME INFORMATION
FROM WANG LIU MEI.
SHE SAYS THE A‐LAWS
KNOW OUR LOCATION.
I'LL TAKE SERAVEE OUT!
WE NEED TO HURRY UP
THE MATCHING PROCESS.
FELDT, GO AND HELP IAN.
ROGER THAT.
ENEMY FORCE APPROACHING!
PREPARE FOR COMBAT!
NO WAY.
THEY'RE GOING INTO
BATTLE NOW?
Mileina:
OPENING HATCH ON DECK TWO!
MOVING SERAVEE TO
CATAPULT DECK.
INCREASING LINEAR CATAPULT
VOLTAGE FROM 230 TO 520.
SUIT IS STABILIZED
WITHIN FIELD.
TRANSFERRING TIMING CONTROL OF
LAUNCH SEQUENCE TO SERAVEE.
ROGER THAT.
SERAVEE,
TIERIA ERDE, LAUNCHING!
ENEMY FORMATION.
ARE THOSE
A‐LAWS MOBILE SUITS?
SETSUNA, WHAT'S OUR CURRENT
FIGHTING STRENGTH?
WE JUST HAVE
TIERIA'S UNIT RIGHT NOW.
HOWEVER, WE HAVE ANOTHER UNIT
THAT'S ALMOST READY
TO ROLL OUT.
JUST TWO UNITS!
PRETTY LEAN LITTLE GROUP
YOU'RE RUNNING HERE, FRIEND.
(Concerned sigh)
(Gasps)
MR. AEON!
WE'RE RECEIVING AN EMERGENCY
CODED MESSAGE FROM MISS NORIEGA.
NORIEGA?
FROM MISS SUMERAGI?!
IT'S A TACTICAL PLAN.
SCHEDULED TO BEGIN IN 0032.
THAT'S A LITTLE
UNREASONABLE.
GOOD WORK, SETSUNA.
HE REALLY DID MANAGE TO
BRING HER BACK.
Zinin:
ENEMY VESSEL SIGHTED.
ONE MOBILE SUIT CONFIRMED.
THAT'S THE GUNDAM
THAT GOT ALAGGA,
AND ITS TRANSPORT SHIP.
TEAM TWO,
DESTROY THE TRANSPORT!
ALL OTHER UNITS, ON THE GUNDAM!
Pilot:
CAPTAIN!
FROM THE TRANSPORT!
Zinin:
HUH?
THEY'RE...THEY'RE JUST MINES.
THEY WON'T EVEN SCRATCH‐‐
(Screams)
THEY'RE DISRUPTING OUR SENSORS?!
ARE THEY TRYING TO
BUY MORE TIME?!
ADJUST COURSE!
WE'LL GO AROUND!
FOLLOW ROUTE ST27.
ROGER.
I SEE YOUR PLAN.
THAT MAKES A LOT OF SENSE.
Tieria:
SERAVEE, INTERCEPTING TARGETS.
CHARGING WITH HIGH DENSITY
COMPRESSED PARTICLES.
GN BAZOOKA,
COMPRESSED PARTICLES,
RELEASING!
Zinin:
TEAM TWO,
ATTACK THE SPACESHIP!
I'LL KEEP THE GUNDAM
OCCUPIED FOR NOW!
IAN!
SEND OUT THE 00!
JUST WAIT A MINUTE, SETSUNA!
WE'RE NOT DONE!
THERE'S NO TIME!
YOU TAKE THE CONTROLS.
WH‐WHAT THE HELL?!
I AM NOW PREPARING TO
DOCK THE SHUTTLE.
ALSO, I'M INITIATING
THE 00'S LAUNCH SEQUENCE.
Mileina:
OPENING HATCH ON DECK ONE!
THAT MUST BE
CELESTIAL BEING'S SHIP.
Mileina:
MOVING 00 TO CATAPULT DECK.
DAMN IT! GIVE ME A BREAK!
(Thinking)
00.
0 GUNDAM'S AND EXIA'S
SOLAR REACTORS
ARE IN THAT SUIT!
THIS IS MY GUNDAM!
THE TWIN DRIVE SYSTEM,
WILL IT WORK?
00'S NOT READY,
SETSUNA!
I'M USING TRANS‐AM.
BUT THAT'S CRAZY,
DON'T DO IT!
ACTIVATING TRANS‐AM!
THAT BOY'S INSANE.
IT'S STILL NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
THE PARTICLE FUSION RATE
CAN'T SEEM TO MAKE IT PAST 73%!
NOT EVEN WITH THE TRANS‐AM!
Mileina:
TWO ENEMY MOBILE SUITS
ARE CLOSING FAST!
WHERE'S 00?!
PLEASE, WAKE UP, 00.
THE 0 GUNDAM IS IN HERE!
AND EXIA!
AND ME!
IT'S BEEN ACTIVATED!
THE SQUARING HAS A TIME LAG!
THE TWIN DRIVE HAS REACHED
THE STABLE OPERATIONAL RANGE!
D‐DID WE GET IT?
WHAT'S THAT LIGHT?
(Startled gasp)
(Tense gasp)
NOW WHAT?
WHAT SYSTEM IS THAT?
THIS IS 00 GUNDAM,
SETSUNA F. SEIEI,
I'M HEADING OUT!
IT'S A NEW MODEL!
THE AHEADS WILL
TAKE CARE OF IT!
00, READY TO ELIMINATE TARGETS!
WHA‐WHAT'S GOING ON?!
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT FEATURE?!
THEN TRY THIS!
(Irritated grunt)
NOW YOUR BEAM WEAPONS
WILL BE USELESS!
Pilot:
AND IN CLOSE COMBAT,
THE ADVANTAGE IS MINE!
DON'T YOU KNOW?
THIS IS OUR...
GUNDAM!
SETSUNA.
SO THAT'S THE REAL POWER
OF A GUNDAM.
SETSUNA.
THE ENEMY MOBILE SUITS!
IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE RETREATING!
GUNDAM.
Regene:
RIBBONS, WHAT KIND OF
GN DRIVE WAS THAT?
YOU DON'T KNOW?
EVEN YOU, THE ONE
WHO CONTROLS LEVEL SEVEN?
ANOTHER SURPRISE,
AEOLIA SCHENBERG.
♪
Feldt:
WELCOME BACK,
MISS SUMERAGI!
LONG TIME NO SEE,
MISS NORIEGA!
THE SAME RECKLESS TACTICS
AS ALWAYS.
I'M NOT SURE ABOUT...
(Shocked gasp)
LOCKON?!
(Gasps)
LOCKON! YOU'RE ALIVE!
NOW THAT'S ONE HELL
OF A WELCOME!
WHAT'S THE DEAL?!
THIS IS HIS YOUNGER BROTHER.
LOCKON STRATOS.
(Angry grunt)
NO. THAT MAN ISN'T HIM.
00 HAS BEEN ACTIVATED.
MARIE.
Narrator:
IN AN EFFORT TO RESCUE
THE CAPTURED MEISTER,
THE DEJECTED
TACTICAL FORECASTER
PLUNGES BACK INTO WAR.
NEXT EPISODE:
"ALLELUJAH RESCUE OPERATION".
BECAUSE SHE DOESN'T WANT TO
LOSE ANYONE ANYMORE.