(Shocked gasp)
AZADISTAN IS...
EVERYTHING'S BURNING!
Marina:
BUT WHY IS AZADISTAN... WHY?!
THE SCALE...
NOT TERRORISTS.
(Startled gasp)
Setsuna:
IT'S A GUNDAM!
AND THAT COLOR!
IS IT HIM?!
Al‐Saachez:
THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU GUESSED RIGHT, PUNK!
♪
Soldier:
BRING THE WOUNDED OVER HERE!
HEY, POINT THAT LIGHT
THE OTHER WAY.
THEY'LL FIND US!
SO MUCH DESTRUCTION.
Abed:
WHAT HAPPENED?
Yael:
BANG! KA‐BOOM!
DON'T BRING
THE CHILDREN OUT HERE!
PLEASE, STAY IN THE SHELTER
FOR A WHILE.
(Gasps)
ALL RIGHT!
SHIRIN!
KLAUS!
OH, KLAUS.
YOU MADE IT THROUGH OKAY.
YEAH, SOMEHOW.
BUT OUR BASE IS...
WELL, YOU CAN SEE FOR YOURSELF.
WE SPENT OVER THREE YEARS
BUILDING EVERYTHING HERE
AND NOW IT'S ALL...
(Sighs)
Katharon leader:
DID YOU BASTARDS
LEAK OUR LOCATION TO THEM?!
WE DID NOTHING OF THE SORT.
Soldier:
THIS IS YOUR FAULT!
YOU GUYS KILLED OUR BUDDIES!
(Aggressive grunt)
KNOCK IT OFF!
THEY DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
HOW DO I KNOW THAT?!
BELIEVE ME!
BUT THEY'RE...
THEY'RE MY BUDDIES!
WE WERE JUST LAUGHING IT UP,
MINUTES AGO!
I HEAR YOU.
WE WILL AVENGE THEM.
I WONDER.
WHO DID TELL THE A‐LAWS?
(Shuddering)
(Startled gasp)
(Gasps)
WHAT DID YOU DO?
I...I JUST‐‐
SO YOU CAUSED THIS.
WHO ARE YOU REALLY?
AN A‐LAWS SPY?
NO!
I'M NOT!
I'M JUST...
(Sighs)
WELL, SAJI CROSSROAD,
LET'S HEAR YOUR EXPLANATION.
(Nervous grunt)
JUST TERRIBLE.
DID THEY HAVE TO BE
SO RUTHLESS?
DAMN A‐LAWS.
MILEINA, DON'T LOOK.
OH, ALL RIGHT,
THEN.
WE LIVE FOR HIS SAKE,
AND WE DIE FOR HIS SAKE.
IF THIS IS TO BE MY FATE‐‐
(Shocked gasp)
IF THIS IS
TO BE MY FATE,
IT IS POINTLESS TO RESIST IT.
Emilio:
WE LIVE FOR HIS SAKE...
IT'S POSSIBLE
THEY COULD BE FRIENDLIES.
Emilio:
AND WE DIE FOR HIS SAKE.
(Panting)
Emilio:
IF THIS IS TO BE MY FATE,
IT IS POINTLESS TO RESIST IT.
THEY WEREN'T ENEMIES!
Emilio:
WE TRAVEL A ROAD
WE CANNOT SEE,
AND WHAT LIES
AT THE END OF THE ROAD
IS THE END OF LIFE.
AND ALL OF THIS
IS THE GUIDANCE OF GOD.
(Gasps)
EMILIO.
(Sobs)
EMILIO!
(Dizzy sigh)
HUH?
H‐HEY!
MISS SUMERAGI,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
MISS SUMERAGI?
(Slaps face)
HOW COULD YOU?
HOW COULD YOU DO
SOMETHING SO FOOLISH?!
I DIDN'T THINK SOMETHING
LIKE THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
I DIDN'T THINK...
I JUST WANTED TO GET AS FAR AS
POSSIBLE FROM THE FIGHTING!
NOTHING LIKE THIS.
THIS WASN'T WHAT I‐‐
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO TOOK
THEIR LIVES, YOU KNOW!
(Shocked gasp)
THROUGH YOUR OWN
FOOLISH ACTIONS!
"OH, I'M DIFFERENT.
NOTHING TO DO WITH ME.
IT'S ALL HAPPENING
IN A DIFFERENT WORLD."
IGNORING REALITY LIKE THAT
IS JUST A KIND OF
INADVERTENT MALICE.
AND THEN
THINGS LIKE THIS HAPPEN!
(Sobbing)
I DIDN'T...
MEAN FOR THIS.
(Weeping)
TIERIA‐‐
SETSUNA.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
OUT THERE?
IT WAS THE WORK
OF THE A‐LAWS.
AND IT ALL HAPPENED
BECAUSE OF HIM.
(Weeping)
SAJI CROSSROAD.
YOU DIDN'T GO BACK
TO AZADISTAN?
(Sobs)
SHIRIN! AZADISTAN IS...
OUR HOMELAND...
OUR HOMELAND IS...
AZADISTAN?
Rindt:
ALTHOUGH WE LOST TWO OF
OUR UNITS
THANKS TO
THE MEDDLING OF THE GUNDAMS,
WE DID SUCCEED IN SMASHING THE
SECRET BASE OF THE DISSIDENTS.
THIS IS SURE TO EARN US
BOTH COMMENDATIONS,
COLONEL MANNEQUIN.
OH, SHUT UP.
OH.
YOU DON'T CARE FOR
MOPPING‐UP OPERATIONS.
I ABSOLUTELY LOVE THEM.
YOU'RE SAYING THAT
YOU ENJOY MURDERING PEOPLE?!
WHY ARE YOU GETTING SO WORKED UP
ABOUT THIS OPERATION?
YOU'VE DONE THINGS SIMILAR TO
THIS IN THE PAST, HAVEN'T YOU?
GOODNESS ME,
THERE WAS THAT
ONE UNFORTUNATE INCIDENT.
FALSE INFORMATION LEADING TO
A BATTLE BETWEEN ALLIES.
I BELIEVE AT THE TIME
YOU WERE A TACTICAL FORECASTER
FOR THE AEU.
SHUT UP!
RAISING YOUR HAND
AGAINST AN ALLY ONCE AGAIN?
I WOULD NEVER FEEL LIKE
PARTICIPATING IN A WAR AGAIN
AFTER AN EXPERIENCE
LIKE THAT.
SO, I HAVE TROUBLE
UNDERSTANDING WHY.
(Clears throat)
IT'S AN HONOR WORKING WITH YOU,
COLONEL MANNEQUIN.
Tieria:
AZADISTAN WAS ATTACKED?
WAS IT THE FEDERATION?
I'M NOT SURE.
BUT AMONG THE MOBILE SUITS
THAT MADE THE ATTACK,
THERE WAS A GUNDAM.
THERE WAS A GUNDAM?
YOU KNOW WHICH ONE IT IS.
(Allelujah gasps)
IT APPEARS THAT
MISS SUMERAGI FAINTED.
SHE WHAT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT WE HAVE ORDERS TO
RETURN TO THE PTOLEMY.
ALL RIGHT.
HEAD BACK.
YOU'RE COMING.
IF WE LEAVE YOU HERE,
YOU MIGHT BE IN
SERIOUS DANGER.
MOST OF THE MAJOR FACILITIES
IN THE CITIES
WERE REDUCED TO RUBBLE.
THERE ARE NO FUNCTIONING POLICE
OR ARMY PERSONNEL LEFT.
BUT EVEN SO,
MY COUNTRY NEEDS ME.
RASA ENTRUSTED ME WITH IT!
COMING BACK HERE
WAS A GOOD IDEA.
(Gasps)
SETSUNA INSISTED.
THEN WE SHOULD
THANK HIM FOR THAT.
FOR WHAT?!
I DON'T CARE ABOUT MY LIFE!
FOR AZADISTAN
I WOULD GLADLY...
GIVE MY...
(Sobs)
MARINA.
(Marina crying)
CELESTIAL BEING SAYS
IT'LL PROVIDE YOU WITH
ANY FOOD OR SUPPLIES
YOU MIGHT REQUIRE
IN GETTING OUT OF HERE.
UNTIL YOU ACTUALLY GET
SET UP IN ANOTHER BASE,
WE'LL PROVIDE YOU
WITH PROTECTION.
IS THAT RIGHT?
TELL THEM THAT WE APPRECIATE
THEIR ASSISTANCE.
JUST WHO WAS IT THAT LEAKED
THE INFORMATION ABOUT OUR BASE?
I'M THE SPY AND
YOU'RE ASKING ME THAT?
Liu Mei:
HOW VERY KIND OF
THE REBORN CELESTIAL BEING.
I WONDER WHO COULD BE
INFLUENCING THEM.
MY MISTRESS,
LET ME TAKE CARE OF THIS.
I'M GOING TO HAVE
NENA TRINITY DO IT.
WHY'S THAT?
CAN YOU USE
QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES?
I DON'T.
Liu‐Mei:
IN ORDER TO DECEIVE
THE INNOVATORS,
THAT GIRL'S ABILITIES
ARE ABSOLUTELY ESSENTIAL.
YOU'RE SIMPLY NOT IN
THE SAME LEAGUE, HONG LONG.
OR RATHER,
ELDER BROTHER.
IS HE RIGHT?
AM I NO DIFFERENT FROM HIM?
Feldt:
DUE TO A MENTAL SHOCK
OF SOME KIND,
SHE'S TEMPORARILY UNCONSCIOUS.
GIVE HER SOME TIME AND
SHE SHOULD WAKE UP ON HER OWN.
WHAT ON EARTH HAPPENED
TO MISS SUMERAGI?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT ONE THING
I DO KNOW IS THAT
IT WAS SOMEHOW TRIGGERED BY
THIS LATEST MASSACRE.
EMILIO.
I HAVE A LOT OF FAITH IN
YOUR TACTICAL FORECASTS.
YOU EACH MADE
YOUR TACTICAL PREDICTIONS
BASED ON FALSE INFORMATION.
AND AS A RESULT,
ALLIED SOLDIERS WOUND UP
FIGHTING AGAINST EACH OTHER.
I RESPECT YOUR EFFORTS A LOT.
YOU FACE THE REALITY OF WAR
AND TRY HARD TO BRING IT
TO AN EARLIER CONCLUSION.
IT WAS JUST A CASE OF YOU
DOING YOUR JOBS TOO WELL,
MANNEQUIN,
MY DEAR EMILIO.
Officer:
KUJO.
(Shocked gasp)
(Thinking)
THE GUNDAMS' TACTICS ARE
JUST LIKE HER STYLE!
COULD KUJO BE...
(Rapid gunfire)
WAS IT JUST...
NO, THAT IS WHAT
A REAL BATTLEFIELD LOOKS LIKE.
HUH?
A CODED MESSAGE
FROM THE COLONEL?
WHY IS IT IN A FORMAT USED ONLY
BY THE OLD CHOBU TEAM?
Sergei:
I'M SORRY FOR
GETTING THIS MESSAGE TO YOU
IN SUCH A COMPLICATED WAY,
BUT I DIDN'T WANT THE A‐LAWS
TO TAKE NOTICE.
I HEARD YOU WERE INVOLVED
IN THE KATHARON
ELIMINATION MISSION.
I'M AFRAID I'M THE ONE
WHO HAS TO APOLOGIZE
FOR WHAT TRANSPIRED
IN CONNECTION WITH THAT.
APOLOGIZE?
HUH?
THAT MOPPING‐UP OPERATION
WAS CARRIED OUT
BECAUSE OF INFORMATION
THE COLONEL OBTAINED?
THAT'S AWFUL.
THE COLONEL MUST BE
FILLED WITH REGRET RIGHT NOW,
AND YET HE'S STILL WORRIED ABOUT
HOW I'M FEELING.
YOU'D LIKE TO ADOPT ME, SIR?
YES, BUT...
ONLY WITH YOUR APPROVAL,
OF COURSE.
(Gasps)
BUT I JUST‐‐
I GUESS SOMA SMIRNOV
MAY NOT EXACTLY BE
THE MOST ATTRACTIVE OF NAMES.
THAT'S NOT TRUE!
BUT... BUT SIR,
I GUESS I WOULD FEEL
A LITTLE LONELY
LOSING THE NAME PERIES.
ARE YOU FOND OF THAT NAME?
I JUST DON'T WANT TO
FORGET THAT PEOPLE
USED TO CALL ME BY THAT NAME.
(Sniffles)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, COLONEL.
THANKS TO YOU, SIR,
I'VE BEEN REMINDED THAT
I AM SUPER SOLDIER NUMBER ONE
OF THE SUPERHUMAN
SPECIAL DUTY INSTITUTE.
I'M A WEAPON,
A TOOL FOR KILLING PEOPLE.
I DON'T DESERVE TO
KNOW HAPPINESS!
(Teary gasp)
Rindt:
YOU SCREWED UP,
COLONEL SMIRNOV.
YOU ALLOWED
THE KATHARON MEMBER TO ESCAPE.
WITH HIM GONE,
THERE WAS NO POINT IN
HAVING US COME OUT HERE!
(Grunts)
COLONEL!
HE'S A SUPERIOR OFFICER!
AND WE ARE MEMBERS OF
THE GOVERNMENT'S
AUTONOMOUS
PEACEKEEPING FORCE.
DON'T THINK THAT OUR RANKS
ARE THE SAME
AS THOSE OF
THE FEDERATION FORCES.
I'M TERRIBLY SORRY.
I ACCEPT FULL RESPONSIBILITY
FOR WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU SHALL REMAIN ON DUTY UNTIL
OUR SUPERIORS DECIDE
THE BEST WAY TO HANDLE THIS.
SIR.
HMM.
ATTACK ON AZADISTAN.
FEDERATION SETS OUT TO
REORGANIZE MIDDLE EAST.
HUH?
AH, LOOK!
THEY REALLY DID A NUMBER HERE!
WHATEVER! WHATEVER!
ALL RIGHT!
IT'S TIME TO GET TO WORK!
Zinin:
CAPTAIN BARACK ZININ
AND TEAM MEMBERS
REPORTING FOR
RESERVE DUTY, MA'AM.
I'M KATI MANNEQUIN.
CAPTAIN, WHY DID YOU
JOIN THE A‐LAWS?
MA'AM!
I VOLUNTEERED TO BECOME
THE FOUNDATION OF
THE UNITED WORLD
WE'RE TRYING TO BUILD.
AND YOU HAVE NO REGRETS?
NONE, MA'AM.
I SEE.
HOW'S MISS SUMERAGI DOING?
SHE HASN'T WOKEN UP.
SHE MAY NEED TO STAY IN BED
FOR A WHILE.
SO, WHAT'S THE LATEST
ON KATHARON?
I'LL PUT IT ON THE MONITOR.
Mileina:
THE KATHARON MEMBERS WILL BEGIN
EVACUATING AT 1200 AS PLANNED.
THE A‐LAWS WILL BE BACK.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
WE KNOW THAT.
WE'LL SEND OUT THE GUNDAMS.
BUT WHAT ABOUT OUR STRATEGY?
IN THIS SITUATION,
WITH MISS SUMERAGI UNCONSCIOUS‐‐
Lasse:
EVEN SO,
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
WE'LL MOVE PTOLEMY
OVER TO THE COASTLINE.
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
THE ENEMY DETECTS ONLY US.
Mileina:
ROGER THAT!
PTOLEMAOIS, TAKING OFF.
HUH?
IN RETALIATION FOR THE
AUTONOMOUS PEACEKEEPING FORCE'S
SUPPRESSION OPERATION AGAINST
THE DISSIDENT GROUP,
ACTS OF TERRORISM
ARE OCCURRING WORLDWIDE.
MY ACTIONS BROUGHT THIS ON.
HOW CAN I...
FIX THIS?
(Shuddering)
KINUE.
LOUISE.
DISENGAGING OPTICAL CAMOUFLAGE.
Mileina:
ESTIMATING APPROXIMATELY 0037
UNTIL OBSERVATION SATELLITES
SPOT US.
Lasse:
ALL HANDS TO
PRIMARY BATTLE STATIONS!
Feldt:
ROGER!
I'M A SUPER SOLDIER.
I MUST CARRY OUT MY DUTY
NO MATTER WHAT IT IS.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
I EXIST AT ALL.
HUH?
SORRY, AM I
INTERRUPTING?
NO.
(Gasps)
PARDON ME, MA'AM.
WHO ARE YOU?
WARRANT OFFICER
LOUISE HALEVY,
ASSIGNED HERE AS
RESERVE PERSONNEL.
I AM LIEUTENANT
SOMA PERIES,
CURRENTLY ASSIGNED
TO THE MOBILE SUIT UNIT.
I'M TERRIBLY SORRY,
LIEUTENANT.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
SPOKEN TO YOU SO CASUALLY.
I DON'T MIND.
YOU'RE PUSHING YOURSELF
TOO HARD.
WHAT?
I CAN SENSE IT WITH
MY QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES.
IN YOUR HEART, YOU'RE CRYING.
NO, THAT'S NOT...
YOU'VE BEEN THINKING A LOT
ABOUT SOMEONE.
Andrei:
LIEUTENANT!
I THOUGHT I MIGHT FIND YOU HERE.
IT'S TIME FOR OUR BRIEFING.
(Gasps)
YOU ARE?
WARRANT OFFICER
LOUISE HALEVY.
UH...
LIEUTENANT.
IT'S YOUR TURN.
UGH! RIGHT.
SECOND LIEUTENANT
ANDREI SMIRNOV.
SHE'S SO YOUNG!
THE OBSERVATION SATELLITES
HAVE LOCATED CELESTIAL BEING.
ALL MOBILE SUIT TEAMS WILL
FOLLOW TACTICAL PLAN E3‐‐
I'LL DEAL WITH
THE "DOUBLE POWERED" GUNDAM
WITH THE SHOULDER ENGINES
MYSELF.
NO ONE IS TO ASSIST
OR INTERFERE WITH ME.
I'M SORRY, WHAT?
A FINE IDEA,
ISN'T IT, COLONEL?
THIS IS THE MAN WITH
THE LICENSE,
THE FABLED MR. BUSHIDO.
I, FOR ONE, WOULD LIKE TO SEE
HIS ABILITIES FIRST HAND.
I'LL BE SURE TO MEET
YOUR EXPECTATIONS.
THANK YOU.
(Door opens and closes)
WE'RE COMMENCING
THE OPERATION!
Lasse:
I KNOW THEY SAW US,
IT'S ABOUT TIME
THEY STARTED HEADING THIS WAY.
SEND OUT THE GUNDAMS!
DECK ONE AND DECK TWO,
OPENING HATCHES.
Feldt:
SERAVEE, ARIOS,
PREPARE TO LAUNCH.
INCREASING LINEAR
CATAPULT VOLTAGE.
TRANSFERRING TIMING CONTROL
OF LAUNCH SEQUENCE
TO SERAVEE.
ROGER THAT.
SERAVEE, TIERIA ERDE,
LAUNCHING!
EVEN WITHOUT
QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES...
YOU HAVE CONTROL NOW!
I HAVE CONTROL NOW!
ARIOS, ALLELUJAH HAPTISM,
COMMENCING
INTERCEPTION OPERATION.
Feldt:
NEXT UP IS CHERUDIM.
00, PLEASE STANDBY.
HARO.
I'M IN SERIOUS MODE TODAY.
ROGER! ROGER!
Feldt:
LINEAR SYSTEM CLEAR.
TRANSFERRING TIMING CONTROL
OF LAUNCH SEQUENCE.
CHERUDIM, LOCKON STRATOS,
TARGETED AND FIRING!
Ian:
SETSUNA, DON'T USE
THE TRANS‐AM.
ROGER THAT.
THAT GUNDAM.
NO, I HAVE TO FOCUS
ON THIS BATTLE.
THIS IS 00,
SETSUNA F. SEIEI,
LAUNCHING!
YOU'RE TRYING TO PROTECT
THE KATHARON PEOPLE, RIGHT?
PLEASE, LET ME HELP,
I'LL DO ANYTHING!
ALL YOU CAN DO IS
WISH US GOOD LUCK, OKAY?
CONFIRMING
MOBILE SUIT FORMATION,
PROBABLY A‐LAWS.
WE'LL BE ENTERING
COMBAT AIRSPACE ANY MINUTE.
I'VE GOTTA DO SOMETHING.
Zinin:
FOUR GUNDAMS HAVE BEEN SIGHTED.
WE'LL BREAK INTO TEAMS AND
TAKE DOWN EACH GUNDAM
SEPARATELY.
WE'LL LEAVE THE DOUBLE‐DRIVE
GUNDAM TO YOU, MR. BUSHIDO.
Graham:
THAT'S EXACTLY AS IT SHOULD BE.
OUR TEAM'S TARGET IS
THE WINGED ONE.
ROGER THAT,
LIEUTENANT PERIES.
THE TIME HAS FINALLY COME.
FOR MOM, FOR DAD.
Zinin:
GUNDAMS SPOTTED!
ALL MACHINES, BEGIN YOUR ATTACK!
(Pilot yelling aggressively)
BULL'S EYE!
LIKE I TOLD YOU,
I'M IN SERIOUS MODE.
I KNOW THIS FEELING!
TEST SUBJECT E‐57!
COULD IT BE?!
Allelujah:
(Gasps)
MARIE, IS IT YOU?!
LIEUTENANT!
STOP INTERFERING!
Andrei:
WARRANT OFFICER HALEVY!
THE AUTO‐FIRE BOMBARDMENT
ISN'T HITTING ANYTHING!
DAMN IT!
IF ONLY LICHTY WAS HERE
TO RUN THINGS!
I'LL HEAD TO THE SUB‐BRIDGE AND
TAKE OVER THE BOMBARDMENT!
YOU, OLD MAN?!
YOU FOCUS ON HANDLING THE SHIP!
ROGER!
THEY SHOW THEMSELVES ON PURPOSE
AND THEN ATTACK FULL FORCE?!
TWO MOBILE SUITS DOWN,
MA'AM!
VERY WELL,
SWITCH TO TACTICAL PLAN C!
ROGER!
IS THIS WHAT KUJO WOULD DO?
Operator:
COLONEL! IT'S MR. BUSHIDO!
I'M PICKING UP A MACHINE
MAKING A DIRECT CHARGE FOR 00!
IT'S EXTREMELY FAST!
(Tense gasp)
Setsuna:
IT'S THAT NEW MODEL!
YOUR SHOOTING HAS IMPROVED, TOO.
Setsuna:
(Aggressive yell)
Graham:
THAT'S THE SPIRIT, BOY!
(Growls)
TEAM LEADER! WARRANT OFFICER
HALEVY IS HEADING FOR THE SHIP!
WHAT?!
I'M GOING TO GO SUPPORT HER!
MR. VASHTI!
LET ME DO SOMETHING TO
HELP YOU GUYS!
ARE YOU AWARE OF THE RISK?
ALL I WANT TO DO
IS PROTECT THOSE PEOPLE.
HMM.
ALL RIGHT! FOLLOW ME!
RIGHT!
(Gasps)
Zinin:
SUCKER!
JUST LIKE A‐LAWS!
THESE GUYS ARE GOOD!
SO YOU KNOW
HOW IT WORKS RIGHT?
UH, YEAH.
(Warning beeps)
Feldt:
TWO MACHINES ARE CLOSING IN
ON THE SHIP!
THOSE TWO BROKE THROUGH!
Ian:
FIRE! SHOOT AT THEM!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
FIRE!
Saji, in memory:
KILLING SOMEONE WOULD MAKE ME
THE SAME AS YOU GUYS.
Ian:
WHAT'S WRONG? HURRY UP!
BUT IF YOU FIGHT,
MORE INNOCENT PEOPLE
WILL BE HURT!
(Trembling gasp)
Saji:
NO, DON'T!
IT'S ONLY NATURAL FOR PEOPLE
TO HATE YOU FOR WHAT YOU DID!
NO, PLEASE DON'T!
Tieria:
THOSE CHILDREN ARE
YOUR VICTIMS TOO, YOU KNOW.
STAY BACK!
CELESTIAL BEING!
(Gasps)
STAY BACK!
♪
Graham:
(Aggressive yell)
TAKING IT EASY ON ME?
OR IS THIS AN ATTEMPT
TO INSULT ME?!
AT THIS RATE WE'LL...
Allelujah:
PLEASE, MARIE, STOP IT!
IT'S ME, ALLELUJAH!
I AM A SUPER SOLDIER!
Graham:
GUNDAM!
THIS IS YOUR REQUIEM!
Peries:
(Aggressive yell)
(Cries in pain)
(Gasps)
MARIE!
Narrator:
ALLELUJAH AND PERIES
EXPOSE THE PAST.
IT IS A REUNION WITH MARIE.
IT IS A FAREWELL
TO PERIES.
NEXT EPISODE:
"REUNION AND SEPARATION".
"I WANTED TO BE YOUR DAUGHTER."