[NARRATOR] Grappler arms
were originally manipulators
that were attached to EVA craft.
At first, it was
the Chinese pirates
that put the arms' abilities
to new and devious uses.
After the Chinese transports
carried Dragonite
from planet to planet,
the pirates began to
attack their own craft
with surprising intensity.
To the pirates of the era,
arms symbolized the
strength of their ships,
and before long
they incorporated
the arms into their
attack methods.
The Federation Space
Forces became
extremely irate with
this situation,
and began developing
Grappler arms of their own,
bragging that they
planned to formally equip
Space Forces fighters with
them in the near future.
They would be a force
to be reckoned with.
Because of the complicated
manner in which space fighters
used these Grappler arms,
space combat was
clearly impossible without
the aid of powerful computers.
The combination of Grappler arms
and potent computers savagely
pushed human physical
and mental capacity
to their limits,
and those who survived battle
were spoken of with respect.
They were known as "Grapplers."
[HORUS] We have entered the
same orbit as the asteroid.
All right, I'm gonna take us in.
Okay, guys, we're goin' over.
[JIM]
Whoa...
[GENE gasps]
Awesome!
So, this is it.
[MELFINA]
Uh...
That's it... the XGP15A-II.
A special ship, built
with the Pirate's brains
and the Space
Forces' technology.
[HILDA]
Come on, let's go!
Uh, hey! Wait a minute!
Don't just leave us here!
Aw, poor little boy.
I'll hold your hand
if you want me to.
Lay off, will ya!
The XGP... 15A-II.
Melfina, come!
I'm coming!
Check it out!
These controls
are pretty unusual.
[HILDA] Like I told you,
this ship is pretty special.
What's that, Hilda?
[HILDA]
It's an alarm clock.
You mean to tell me, the pirates
and the Space Forces
worked together to
build this thing?
The pirates couldn't
have developed
this ship on their own.
They used money and connections
to get Space Forces to sign on.
But, what in the world
are you doing with a ship
that's hidden in
a place like this?
[HILDA] It's here because
I swiped it from them.
Wow, I'm impressed!
You managed to get on the
bad side of the pirates
and the Space Forces!
[HILDA]
I owed 'em one.
[JIM]
Wow!
[clears throat]
[GENE]
Hm? Hey, What was that sound?
[GILLIAM] Good morning
and good day to you,
Ladies and, of
course, gentlemen.
[GENE]
Who are you?
[GILLIAM] I am myself, but
it is inappropriate for me
to subjectively define who I am.
I lack the means to test the
veracity of any such definition.
And the restraints therefore,
have been placed within me
restricting such a thought.
What the hell kind
of answer is that?
[GILLIAM] The only answer I
have in regards to myself is
that the name that I have been
granted is "Gilliam II,"
and that I have
been authorized
with the maintenance
of this vessel.
Hey! He's the ship's
computer, Gene.
Yeah? Well, why
didn't he say so?
[GILLIAM] Incidentally, just
who might you gentlemen be?
They happen to be
the ship's crew.
[GILLIAM]
One moment, please.
[GILLIAM] Oh, dear.
There seems to be a problem.
It appears there is
nothing regarding this
that has been recorded
in my memory.
Of course not.
You've just recently
been activated.
Just start from now.
[GILLIAM]
One moment, please.
It appears part of my
personal service regulations
file has been deleted.
Shall I attempt to recover it?
No, that's not necessary,
we are the crew.
Obey the orders of the crew.
[GILLIAM]
Understood.
As it stands,
I have no authority to
run a search on you.
This is really tickin' me off!
Just launch the stupid
ship, Gilliam!
Do it right now!
[GILLIAM]
Of course, sir.
Oh, my.
And who might this be?
Interesting.
Personnel recording complete.
However, currently, I am
unable to launch this vessel.
Say what?
Are you tryin' to
tell me you weren't
the ship's navigation computer?
[GILLIAM] I support all
systems of the XGP15A-II,
except matters
pertaining to piloting,
they are outside my control.
Jim, what's with this guy?
Maybe everything's
done manually.
[GILLIAM]
No, that's unlikely.
Melfina will handle it.
--[JIM] Huh?
--[GENE] Huh? Melfina?
Did you say...?
You mean me?
That's right, Melfina.
She will assist you, Gilliam.
[GILLIAM]
Is that so?
Then it is understood.
What's understood?
[GILLIAM]
That you are this ship's crew.
Aww! This is driving me insane!
Gilliam, report the ship status.
[GILLIAM]
Navigation is possible,
but all equipment
is not on board.
[HILDA]
Just so long as you can fly.
[GILLIAM] Crew furnishings
have not been loaded
and food stores are limited
to 10 emergency packs.
Furthermore, the
XGP15A-II has not yet
been appointed a designation.
No name, huh?
How 'bout "Genius James"!
[groans]
Give it a rest.
The ship's name is--
[beeping]
[HORUS]
This is Horus.
Hilda, it's that pirate ship.
Distance, 6,000.
It can't be!
Impossible!
[HORUS] Magnetic aberrations
and enemy ship's
Tao field delayed detection.
It's closing in fast.
All right, Gene, I want you and
the others to launch this ship.
But what about you?
Horus and I will intercept them.
Wouldn't it be better for
all of us to go together?
I don't want the
ship to be stolen.
Melfina knows how to pilot it.
Do it!
Come on, I've felt
like puking for hours!
Quit your whining!
[MELFINA]
Uh...?
[GENE groans] Looks like
I've got no choice...
Gilliam, prepare to launch!
[GILLIAM]
Very well, Gene.
Please sit in the pilot's seat.
Okay!
Uh, what about me?
[GILLIAM]
Over there, Melfina.
I suppose I should sit here?
[GILLIAM]
That's fine, James.
Call me Jim.
Okay, Gilliam, what now?
[GILLIAM] Holding for
Melfina to get ready.
I'll display the control manual,
so please read it
while you're waiting.
What's he mean?
What the heck kind
of system is that?
Your guess is as good as mine!
[HORUS]
I am unable to determine
how the enemy ship
tracked us here.
Some Tao spell.
How are the engines?
[HORUS]
Ether drive Engine is active.
Shall I release the anchor?
They're only after
the XGP and Melfina.
They won't do anything drastic.
Ammunition?
[HORUS]
34% remaining.
We'll attack from right here.
[MELFINA]
Connecting.
Connecting. Connecting.
Connecting...
Connecting.
[MELFINA]
Connection established.
I'll activate the engines.
[GENE] Hey! What the hell
is goin' on here?
Awesome! She's linked
up with the ship.
Well I think she nuts to get
naked at a time like this.
Uh, oh!
[MELFINA]
The engines are sealed!
We need access to them
now or they won't work!
Uh... Where do I, uh...
[GILLIAM]
The engine room, please.
The engine room?
[GILLIAM]
I'll show you the way.
[JIM]
Okay, I'll be right back!
[GENE]
Sure.
Man, this ship is
a royal pain...
[GILLIAM] It only appears
that way, at first.
You might think of it
as if it were still in
its plastic wrapper.
[GENE]
Has it been flight-tested?
[GILLIAM] The engine
itself has been tested,
but there is no record
of it having been tested
after installation.
Ohh, are you kidding me?
[MELFINA]
Bringing up all sensors.
[GILLIAM]
A ship outside is hailing us.
Shall I open a channel, Gene?
Patch her through, right away!
Gene, how much longer?
[GENE]
Don't ask me!
Just picked up a case
of termites, hurry!
[JIM]
Damn, these guys are anal!
[GILLIAM] I'm told it's a
Space Forces tradition.
[OLD MAN]
Oh. So that's it.
Let's go!
[GILLIAM]
Warning.
Intruders have entered the dock.
Say what?!
Lock all guns on Horus.
Once the XGP is secured,
fire at will.
Leave anchors and
accelerate slowly.
We'll rotate the asteroid
and use it as a shield!
[YOUNG GIRL]
Damn you, Hilda!
Trying to protect yourself
with the asteroid!
Separate Grappler Ship!
Take us to the sun side
of the asteroid!
Don't fire at random!
Split up and attack
him from all sides!
Ah!
Gilliam! How do I get
that gate open?!
[GILLIAM] I can have it
opened by remote, Gene.
Open it!
Gilliam, how's it coming?
[GILLIAM] Start-up
preparations are complete.
[GENE]
All right!
[MELFINA] Please start the
engines with the ignition key.
That's easy.
[GILLIAM]
Engines on-line.
Generators operational.
Switching power over from
sub-circuits to main.
[JIM screams]
We're lifting up!
[MELFINA]
All systems green.
Ether Drive Engine standing by.
All right. We'll launch
once that gate's open!
[GILLIAM]
Roger that.
Okay, then. Heh, heh.
Huh?!
What the hell?
What's the gate doing
pointed at the bad guys?
[OLD MAN]
Cut your engines.
[GENE, JIM]
Huh?!
[OLD MAN] If at all possible, we
want that ship left undamaged.
Hilda! We're in trouble here!
[HILDA]
I'm a little busy right now!
Release all anchors!
[groaning] Ah! Dammit!
We have you now, Hilda.
Gilliam!
Where are the weapons?!
[GILLIAM] The Grappler
arms are operational,
but they have no weapons.
We're goin' out!
Uh! But we'll crash into 'em!
It's all right, I'll
come up with somethin'!
[GILLIAM] Please focus
on the task at hand.
That's an order!
[OLD MAN] They're going to
use their Grappler arms!
It will damage the ship,
but we have no choice.
Fire all anchors!
Ahh! Hurry, Gene, hurry!
Uh-oh! Shiit!
[OLD MAN]
What the hell?
What is that?
[MELFINA] I'm picking up
an object on sensors.
[GILLIAM] It's a thermonuclear
missile or shell.
Something of that nature.
What in the hell happened?
[PIRATE PILOT]
We're under attack, sir!
That's... That's
MacDougall's ship!
No! What is MacDougall doing?!
[GENE, JIM grunting]
But why are you doing
this, MacDougall?!
[HILDA]
What are you up to, MacDougall?
Hey, Hilda, it's been
a very long time.
You'll destroy the XGP!
[RON]
That's the general idea.
Die! Die! Die!
Die!
You have double crossed us!
As of now, our contract
with you has ended.
We're carrying out
a new contract now,
and that's all there is to it.
And that contract is
to wipe out the XGP.
[gasping]
[OLD MAN] At this rate,
we won't be able to escape
the star's gravity well!
Come back! Please! Hurry up!
Can you see what's
going on outside?
[GILLIAM] I'm not sure if the
dock's cameras are still active.
Hey, wait.
I know that ship.
I can't believe it. MacDougall.
All right, launch
the halcyon missile.
Yeah! Halcyon missile! [laughs]
This is my way of saying,
good-bye, "Hot Ice" Hilda.
That name of yours has caused us
plenty of unnecessary trouble.
Man, you know brother,
that's totally the waste.
It's okay, we don't
need the XGP.
Remember, we're the ones with
the fastest ship in the galaxy.
I meant Hilda.
Didn't you tell me that
she was really hot?
[RON]
Heh!
Sorry, she's not your type.
All right, let's go back
and report to our client.
[PIRATE PILOT] A gravity
catapult course around Farfallas
would put us too
close to a flare!
The ship will burn up!
Yes, I know that.
All engines max!
Hilda and MacDougall,
you will pay for this,
you damned Outlaws!
[HORUS] We are unable to escape
from Farfallas' gravity well.
Gene! Do you hear me? Come in!
Gene!
Gene, Melfina! Respond!
[yells]
[OLD MAN]
Huh? Hm...
[GILLIAM]
The ship is now in the clear.
[MELFINA]
Stabilizing attitude.
Once we're stabilized,
bring engines to full!
[GILLIAM]
If you do it all at once,
the engines may not
become stable.
What's more important here, the
engines or the whole damn ship?!
[GILLIAM]
Well, then. Feel free.
Let's rock!
What kind of ship is that...?
That ship has four
Unsen engines.
Very well, prepare for
close-quarters combat!
We'll board them
our Grappler arms!
Prep the lander for launch!
I'm going over!
[MELFINA]
Engine output, 81%.
We've exceeded Farfallas'
escape velocity.
Where's Horus?
Gene! The pirate ship! Look!
[JIM screams]
Don't mess with me, bastards!
[OLD MAN groans, screams]
Hilda! Come in!
Grab me!
[HILDA screams]
Hilda! No!
[GENE]
Hilda! Are you okay?!
Dammit!
I can't make it! You'll
have to come save me!
[GENE]
Come save you?
[HILDA]
Hurry up!
Well, can we do it, Melfina?
[MELFINA]
If we decelerate,
we'll drop below
escape velocity.
[GILLIAM]
And we can't accelerate now
because of that pirate ship.
If you don't do something,
we'll fall into the star.
C'mon, Gene, yank off
that wire, will ya?!
[HILDA]
Wait!
Listen, don't cut
that anchor yet.
Sorry, but I have to
leave you, Horus.
[HORUS]
I understand. Goodbye, Hilda.
Move on it, Hilda!
[MELFINA]
Increasing output.
85... 86... 87...
[YOUNG GIRL]
Hilda!
Huh?
[YOUNG GIRL chanting]
[chanting]
Help, Gene...
[YOUNG GIRL screams]
[HILDA screams]
Hilda, I'm coming,
hang in there!
[GILLIAM]
You mustn't.
We'll just fall into
Farfallas as well.
What about the ship's anchor?
[GILLIAM]
The distance is too great.
[GENE growls]
Damn it!
So there's nothing
they can really do...
Huh?
[YOUNG GIRL]
I won't let your people survive!
[chanting]
[gasps]
[YOUNG GIRL]
What're you doing?!
Do not interfere!
Do you still read me, Gene?
Just remember.
Outlaws never go down easy,
no matter what happens to them.
[teeth clenching]
[GILLIAM] We have just exited
Farfallas' gravity well.
[JIM]
Gene...
[GILLIAM]
Gene, please lay in a course.
Before we do that, there's
something I've decided on.
[GILLIAM]
Yes, what is it, Gene?
I've decided to name the ship.
I'm calling it...
...the Outlaw Star !
[GENE] Ctarl-Ctarl comes
right at us out of nowhere!
Wait just a minute,
aren't you--
The poor little thing,
away from home
and abandoned by her people.
This girl Aisha's story is
such a sad and difficult one
that I just find myself
moved to tears!
Yeah, right!
You're barkin' up
the wrong tree, lady!
Next time, on Outlaw Star :
"The Beast-Girl,
Ready To Pounce"!
You better get ready!