[NARRATOR]
When humanity was spreading
their colonies out into
space, as to be expected,
there were many encounters
with alien races.
These encounters sometimes
gave rise to war.
And other times,
discussion ended in
the establishment
of friendly relations.
There are currently
six alien races
that mankind has encountered.
Comparatively speaking,
the Nayans and Corbonites
are friendly towards humans.
The Silgrians, however,
have been considered by
most, to be too friendly.
Humanity's relationship with
the Lorgans is somewhat bad,
and there are obstacles in
even associating with the Sith.
After countless battles
with the Ctarl,
trade treaties were
finally concluded.
As humanity's sphere
of influence expands,
further encounters
probably await them.
There is a lesson to be learned
from the example of the past.
Meetings are merely
the beginning.
Everything begins
with understanding.
One lesson learned from
love can be applied to you.
Encounters are always abrupt.
[phone ringing]
Hello, this is Starwind
and Hawking Enterprises,
can we help you?
Yes, sir.
Yes, we handle
interplanetary transport,
but our ship's payload's
fairly small.
What's the cargo?
Ah! That would be a
problem. I'm sorry.
[GENE]
Yeah. Please call again, sir.
What did he say?
He asked if we could haul some
huge construction equipment
in the Outlaw Star, but come on,
there's no way we
could handle that.
[JIM]
Hmm...
[sighs]
There's gotta be something out
there, some job for us to do.
I posted some really
good ads on the net,
but the responses aren't
even worth mentioning.
Yeah, forget it.
The only thing that those jobs
are worth is chump change.
Gene, we've gotta get a job,
no matter how rotten it is.
Our wallet's in bad shape.
I don't know if we
can be so picky.
[GILLIAM] Spaceport parking fees
are ridiculously expensive.
I know, the parking is
practically on the street,
and it still costs way too much.
[GILLIAM]
It can't be helped.
In the big city like this, we
were lucky to even find a spot.
[JIM]
Ah...
Thanks a lot, Melfina.
Don't mention it.
You still haven't been
able to find any work, Jim?
If Gene wasn't so picky,
we might have some.
Come on, if we don't turn
a profit, what's the point?
[bell rings]
Hey, maybe it's a customer.
How can we help--
How's business doin', everyone?
Oh, it's only you.
Okay, I guess.
Yeah, we've got nothing!
[JIM]
Hmph!
[AISHA laughs]
I knew that. But
there's no problem.
You don't have to
worry about a thing.
That's why you find
me standing here.
I came to offer you two a job.
Oh, yeah? Well, what is it?
Well, they tell me that
in the downtown area
by the Heifong Spaceport,
there's a ferocious animal that
happens to be in the sewers.
Rumor has it it's a
runaway pet or something.
Anyway, the job is
to exterminate it
as soon as possible.
[JIM hums]
[yawns]
[AISHA growls]
What is wrong with you?!
Did you hear anything I said?
I heard you, you expect
us to go into the sewer?
This job smells fishy, Aisha.
Whaddya mean? It was
posted by the Heifong
Municipal Waterworks
Department, so it's legit!
Yeah, but how much does it pay?
Five hundred wong!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Mm-hm.
[JIM grunts]
[AISHA yelps, grunts]
[growls]
What's the big idea?!
Fine, if that's the
way you guys want it,
I'll just go do the job myself!
And you'll be sorry!
[grunts]
When people can't accept a
little kindness gracefully,
it's gonna be all
over for humanity!
Can you believe it? Gimme a
break! What was she thinking?
It's sounds like a 500-wong job.
Hey, Gilliam, what about you?
Have you heard of any good work?
[GILLIAM]
I'm sorry, Gene, but I haven't.
--[beeping]
--Who's that?
Hey look, Gene, it
could be a job offer.
Hi there, Jim! How's
business been going?
Oh, hi, Fred! How ya doin'?
Uh, yeah! Hi, how are ya?
Uh...
If it's about the money we owe
you, we can't pay you back yet.
[FRED]
I figured as much,
so I thought I'd tell you
about a job that's come up.
Actually, a business
associate of mine
has gotten into
some odd trouble.
[JIM]
Uh... What kind?
Well, he brought some cargo
over from the Silgry system.
But when he arrived
here on Heifong,
the cargo had
suddenly disappeared.
And he asked me to get
you two to look into it.
Eh, why doesn't he just
let the cops handle it?
[FRED] That's totally
out of the question!
It's just shy
of smuggling.
Like weapons?
It's a new species of insect.
[GENE]
Sorry, Fred.
--[beep]
--This is not our kind of job.
--Just hold on, Gene!
--[beep]
How much is the
job paying, Fred?
[FRED]
Seven hundred up front,
plus two thousand if the
cargo is returned safely.
Let's take it, come on!
Another chump job like that?
Forget it, I'm not interested.
Fine, I'll take it! Who do
I see and where do I go?
Great! He's a Silgrian.
He'll be on dock eight at
the spaceport right by you.
I'll call ahead and
tell him you're coming.
[groans] I can't believe
you're working for Fred.
Gene, we cannot
afford to be picky!
Hey, a much bigger job will
come along soon; don't worry.
[MELFINA] Jim, do you want
me to come along with you?
Sure, Melfina, that'd be great!
What?! I gotta stick
around here all by myself?
[GILLIAM]
I'm still here, Gene.
[GENE] And what am I
s'posed to do with you, huh?
That big job's comin', right?
Keep an eye out for it!
Heh! You see?
You're gonna regret it!
--[door opens]
--[GILLIAM] See you later, Jim!
[door closes]
[phone rings]
Well, there you have it!
That was quick!
[GENE] Hello, Starwind
and Hawking Enterprises!
Your ad says that you'll
solve any problem.
Is that really true?
That's right! So, what exactly
is it we can help you with?
[VENDOR]
Well, there's something funny
about the ice cream
vender next door!
Uh, what? Did you say ice cream?
[VENDOR] He's gotta be
breaking some kinda law!
How else could he be
making such a killing
when it tastes like that?!
Thanks to him, my business
is in the toilet!
There's something about that
ice cream that isn't normal!
I know it! And I want you--
[GILLIAM] You didn't even
ask him what he would pay.
I am not an investigator.
Huh?
Hm...
[GENE]
Hello.
Remember me?
Yeah, it's Gene.
[GILLIAM] Gene, did you
think of a good job?
[groans] What was that for?!
Yeah, that's right, I promised
you I would, didn't I?
So listen, I was wondering
if we could go out for
dinner or something.
[GILLIAM] And to think
I call that man, Captain.
[SILGRIAN] Hmm... I really
don't know what to make of this.
It happened five days ago.
I had a break after I landed,
and I figured I'd get down to
business, when I noticed that
the container was empty,
just like you see here.
If something isn't done,
I'm'a take a bath on this one!
Come on, now honestly,
what cargo did you have?
All right, Fred
recommended you two,
so I'll let you in on it,
confidentially speaking...
It was an extremely
rare insect and plant.
Well, did you ever think the
insect could've run away?
By opening the container
and the hatch on my ship?
[scoffs]
No, that's simply impossible.
Even if that were the situation,
what about the plant?
Maybe the bug got
hungry and ate it.
[SILGRIAN] Also impossible,
it's carnivorous!
They were stolen.
My crew and I have
looked everywhere,
but as you can see there's
no sign of 'em, none!
Is it true that the police
can't be of any help?
[SILGRIAN]
We can't go to the police
because we didn't apply
for any import entry
for either the insect
or the plant.
Now, you don't need to
worry about a thing.
They don't carry
any harmful viruses
or diseases you can catch.
We've checked all that out,
right here on our own.
You do understand.
It's such a bother to have to
go through all that red tape.
[JIM]
Uh... I guess so.
Come to think of it, now that
I look back on the situation,
I can't imagine why
for the life of me,
I ever took such a giant risk.
[JIM] So, what kinda bug
and plant are they, anyway?
[SILGRIAN]
I'll give you the catalogue
I put together for the sale.
The plant looks and feels like
one of those "cactusy" things
that grows in the world
where y'all are from.
Guess he means a
regular ol' cactus.
[SEWER MAN] My workers said
they saw it right in here,
that's what they said.
The reports that I heard
claimed that it was some
big meat-eating animal.
But that's a little
hard to believe.
You don't have to worry anymore,
Aisha's here to handle it.
Yeah, there's no doubt about it,
we were definitely fortunate
enough to get a Ctarl-Ctarl
to handle this matter.
Well, I'm gonna leave you now,
so you can do your work.
[AISHA]
You can count on me!
All right, monster!
Aisha's coming!
You better stay put
and be a good boy now!
[laughing continues]
[JIM]
We're back!
Hey, Gene? It's you!
Welcome back. Hello there, Jim.
You the only one here?
Where's Gene?
I have no idea. He was
already gone when I arrived.
Huh, I wonder. Maybe there
was a big job that came in.
So, why are you here, Suzuka?
No particular reason.
I just simply decided
I would come by
to see how business
is coming along.
Eh, we're getting by, I guess.
Well, Melfina, I was
just thinking' I should
do a little diggin' in
the pet market over there.
That's a good idea, Jim.
Should I check the
spaceport's security section
and see if anything unusual
happened five days ago?
Yeah! That'd be great.
[chair rattles]
[SUZUKA] You seem to be rather
busy, so I'll be leaving now.
Oh, okay. See you later.
[SUZUKA] Please give Gene
my regards, won't you?
Huh? Hey! Hi!
Hi!
I'm sorry, have you
been waiting long?
No, no problem. I just got here.
So, how you doin'?
You have any free time now?
Well, now that the race is
over, that's all I have.
I still think that was amazing,
a Privateer making fourth
place in his first race.
If we hadn't run into trouble,
we would've been first.
But let's not talk
about that now,
why don't we go get
some tea or something?
[CLAIRE]
Sure.
To tell you the truth,
I still don't know
Heifong City very well.
So how about you? Do you know
of any good places around here?
Yes, let's keep walking and
I'll show you all around.
Sounds great.
[CLAIRE]
So, what are you up to now?
[GENE] Well, we started
our business again,
Starwind and Hawking
Enterprises.
We sell solutions to
any kind of problem.
How's business going?
[GENE]
Okay.
That's right,
how could I forget,
you finished fourth in
the Heifong Space race.
Of course, you're doing well.
Yeah, right.
[CLAIRE] Are you sure you can
take time away to meet me?
My seeing you is much more
important than work-- Huh?
I just got this great idea!
Let's get some ice cream!
I-Ice cream?
Come on, right over there!
I feel like having some all
of a sudden, isn't that funny?
It never used to
be this popular.
Maybe they changed the recipe.
It's sounds great!
For some reason, I feel
like having some, too.
Oh, good! I'll go
buy us some, then.
Hey, let me get that--
[CLAIRE]
Fourth Place Winner!
It's my treat!
Uh-- Hm...
What the...?
[VENDOR] Well, there's
something funny about
the ice cream vender next door!
[CLAIRE]
Sorry it took so long!
Oh! Hey, thanks a lot.
[GENE]
Hm...
Hey, this ice cream
seems pretty average.
Yeah, I agree.
[BOTH]
Hm... Huh?
[JIM]
Here?
[MELFINA]
That's right.
Five days ago, the fence around
here was completely bent.
But, now it looks like
they've already fixed it.
And the security systems?
They are equipped with both
infrared detectors
and metal detectors,
but it appears as though
nothing has set them off.
Yeah, I guess they could be
set off by a measly old insect.
[MELFINA]
So, maybe it did run away.
[JIM]
Maybe.
If it's a whole meter long,
maybe a bug that size
would a have a brain.
And if that's true...
...what are those?
They say they're the wastewater
drains for the spaceport.
They're supposed to be
connected to the sewer.
To the sewer? Wait a minute.
Wasn't it Aisha who mentioned
something about a sewer?
♪ I'm on my way, I'm on my
way, to get the monster! ♪
♪ I'm... on... my... way! ♪
♪ To get the monster!
To get the monste-- ♪
[screams]
Hey, what's goin' on here,
what's the big idea?!
What the heck is
this stuff? Huh?
[stammers, screams]
[JIM]
That's right!
The job you have, you know, to
kill some animal in the sewers?
[SEWER MAN]
Oh sure, but I've already
put somebody on that job.
Tell me, was it a
female Ctarl-Ctarl?
[SEWER MAN]
Oh, you know her?
Listen it's real important,
I need you to tell me
where she's looking,
and how it's connected to the
sewer lines from the spaceport.
[GENE]
Man, that seems strange.
I wonder why that ice cream man
is selling so much more ice
cream than the other guy,
when his ice cream doesn't
even taste that good?
You do have a point.
Oh well, who cares,
let's forget about it.
It's not like ice cream
is the only thing
Heifong is famous for?
Sure, there are plenty of
other things to do here.
You haven't been anywhere, yet?
Not yet. We entered the race
right after we got here.
[CLAIRE]
Where did you live before that?
Sentinel, in the
middle of nowhere.
--[beeping]
--[JIM] Gene! Gene!
Sorry, could you excuse me?
Yeah, what do ya
want? Can't it wait?
[JIM]
No! If we don't stop Aisha,
you can kiss that two
thousand wong goodbye!
What the hell are
you talking about?
[growling]
[JIM] The ferocious animal
she was talking about that
she went to kill in the
sewer is the Silgrian's bug!
Aisha's gonna rip it to
pieces! I just know it!
[GENE] I don't understand
a word you're saying.
[growling]
[hisses]
[growls, roars]
[JIM] I don't know what
happened to the cactus plant,
but I know one thing,
we've gotta capture that bug
before Aisha does!
Cactus plant?
The cactus plant!
[JIM]
Gene! Do you read me?
Hey, Gene!
[ringing]
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
Hey, what the hell
is that thing?
Careful, Claire, stand back!
Okay!
[AISHA yells]
[ringing]
Huh?!
[GENE gasps]
[AISHA]
Gene!
What's the big idea?!
Oh, hey, sorry! What the
hell's she riding on?
Ah! It's coming back again!
[ringing]
[AISHA groans]
What is that?
Gene, what the hell're you
tryin' to do, you bird brain!
Are you trying to kill me?!
[laughs nervously]
No, of course not, Aisha.
You know, you're really
beginning to bug me.
You want some more of me?
All right, you fleabag,
try a little of this!
[JIM]
Gene! Don't!
Huh? Jim?
If we can catch the thing,
it's worth two thousand wong!
It's five hundred
for me if I kill it!
You gotta catch it
before she does!
I gotta kill it!
It's two thousand wong!
I don't care! I'm gonna kill it!
Guys, stop it already!
What the hell are you
two talkin' about?
I've been sensing some
strange high-frequency waves
for some time now.
Like that one.
High-frequency?
[JIM]
That's it!
[groaning]
[JIM yelps]
[GENE]
Jim! Where ya goin'?
[JIM]
I don't know!
That cactus is doing this!
--Ah!
--[gunshot]
[GROUP gasps]
What do you think
you're doing?!
I have no idea!
[CACTUS] So you're beginning
to realize my true nature.
Not bad for a lower creature; I
guess I have to compliment you.
What is the deal!
Why are you talking so weird?
I tellin' you guys, it's not me!
My mouth is moving by itself!
[BOTH gasp]
All right! What in
the hell are you?
[CACTUS]
Ha! You may call me Great One.
I am a higher life form capable
of ruling the entire universe.
No matter what you do,
you have absolutely no means
of escaping my control.
I suggest you surrender.
You cactus bastard!
You were behind all this!
So what exactly is it
that you plan to do?
Why are you selling ice cream,
"Ruler of the Universe"?
That's simple: for observation
and experimentation
to see precisely how effective
my control is over you.
And now, my observation and
experimentation are complete.
[JIM yelps]
Gene!
Hey, wait Jim!
--[ringing]
--[GENE groans]
Oh no! The treacherous
animal is getting away!
[CACTUS] My plan will
proceed to stage two.
[JIM]
No way! Help, Gene!
I'm trying, damn it...
Melfina!
[CACTUS]
Halt, I say! You lower animal!
[CACTUS] Halt! I said,
halt right where you are!
[CACTUS]
Halt! Halt!
Why, damn you!
Why doesn't my
power work on you?!
Stop doing horrible
things to him!
--[JIM yelps]
--[CACTUS groans]
What have you done?!
Hurry! Pick me up!
[JIM gasps]
Uh...
Uh... Uh...
What should I do now?
Squash that thing!
[gasps] You really
want me to squash it?
No, don't do it!
If you squash it, we're gonna
lose tons and tons of money!
Oh...
Do it, Melfina!
Ignore what he's saying.
The cactus still has
control over him!
Oh yeah, right.
Um, sorry, Jim. I have to.
Come on, I'm beggin'
ya. Don't do it!
[CACTUS]
Stop it, damn it!
Stop! I command you! Stop!
Damn you!
No! I told you!
You must obey me!
I belong to a higher species!
What are you doing to me? Stop!
Stop it! Stop, I tell you!
How dare you! How dare you!
You lower animal! Stop!
Stop it! I-I shouldn't have
to beg! I insist you stop!
Please stop! Stop it!
Now, I beg of you!
Please! Stop! Stop!
Please...!
It's all mashed up.
It sure is! Now, you're
not gonna make me eat
anymore of that crappy
ice cream, are you?
Why would you eat
crappy ice cream?
[sirens]
Oh no, now what?!
I'm gonna go and
kill that monster!
I won't let the cops
have all the glory!
Oh great, what a mess. That
Silgrian is gonna take a fall,
and now, we're not gonna
see any money out of it.
Yeah, that's what I would guess.
Well, anyway, I'm amazed
that you could stand up
to that thing's control
like you did, Melfina.
Don't you remember, Gene,
I'm not like normal people.
--Huh?
--I know you're not.
And that's exactly
what saved Jim.
Yeah, he's right about that.
Thanks a lot, Melfina.
Sure.
[JIM]
Looks like that Silgrian was
under the Great One's control
when he brought it here.
They say it was a capsule
that the Space Forces
found in deep space.
And they have no knowledge
of there being any others.
[GILLIAM]
I see.
After all we did, all
we have to show for it
is a 700 wong deposit?!
What about you?
[GENE]
Hm? Who? Me?
Yeah, you were there on
the job, too, weren't you?
Uh, yeah, but you
know what happened,
all that ruckus blew the
whole thing out the window.
Oh, if only... Aw, man...
If it weren't for that lousy
ice cream and that stupid plant,
I would've scored for sure.
--Scored, Gene?
--[GENE stammers]
Yeah, I mean, it's
just an expression,
with that big job, you
know what I'm saying.
[GILLIAM]
Oh, really? You don't say.
Would you just shut
that can of yours
and mind your own
business for once?
[SUZUKA]
Good day.
[BOTH]
How can we help you-- Ugh.
[GENE]
Oh, it's you...
I was just wondering
how business is doing.
Not bad!
It's not doing at all.
--Hmph!
--[GENE groans]
I thought that
might be the case.
That's why I decided to come
by and tell you about a job.
What job?
There's a theme park in the
suburbs outside Heifong City,
and they're looking
for people to perform
in a quick-draw Wild West show.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[SUZUKA yelps]
What's the meaning
of this?! How rude!
I'm telling you, if people can't
accept kindness gracefully,
it's all over for humanity!
I sure hope a good job
--comes in soon.
--[phone rings]
[JIM]
Hello?
I see, sir!
Gene, they need a tugboat!
We'll take it!
We don't have a choice.
I just hope something
else'll turn up soon.
[GENE] We're looking at a little
bomb-defusing action this time!
And I'm afraid to say, my life's
final countdown has begun!
What am I gonna do, damnit?!
I'm no good at
these delicate jobs.
And I'm so stressed out that
I can't even take a leak!
You understand, right?
If I'm not careful... boom!
Next time, on Outlaw Star :
"Final Countdown"!
You better get ready!