[NARRATOR] As vast as
the universe may be,
there is only a handful of
planets which enjoy acclaim
and notoriety as
tourist attractions.
Among these getaways is the
hot springs planet, Tenrei.
Despite its Earth-like setting,
it's a favorite vacation spot
for a wide variety of
intergalactic races.
Lending to Tenrei's appeal
as a holiday destination
is its fascinating origin;
a history colored by legend.
It began over a century ago
with three pioneers who
ventured to this world.
Believing the planet
to be uninhabited,
they came here on a quest
for a mysterious power
called "mana." But instead,
their search lead them
to discover one natural
hot spring after another.
Seemingly overnight,
the beautiful sorceress of
the explorers transformed
the pristine landscape
of rejuvenating waters
into a travelers' paradise!
More than 100 years
after its development,
some say that the early
founders still live.
Only a tourist Mecca could
account for a story like this.
[JIM]
Oh, whoa!
[JIM] Are there really supposed
to be wizards on this planet?
[GENE] I heard there were,
so here we are.
[JIM] But why's everybody
dressed like that?
[BARKER]
Greetings ladies and gentlemen!
Welcome!
All the delights of Hagone
Hot Springs World await you!
[CREW]
Huh?
[BARKER]
Ha, ha, ha! Come along!
You'll need to take care of
some immigration matters first.
Right this way!
--[GENE yelps]
--[crash]
--[JIM yelps]
[MELFINA gasps]
[AISHA]
Hey! What's the big idea?!
[SUZUKA]
How rude! Ahh! Uh.
Huh?! Ahh!
[BARKER] All right, everyone
ready for some fun in the sun?
"Immigration matters," huh?
[AISHA] All we did was
change our clothes!
[BARKER]
Okay!
Please enjoy your
visit here, everyone!
[FEMALE PA]
Attention.
An uphill train will be
arriving shortly on track two.
To ensure your safety,
please stand behind
the white line while
on the platform.
[JIM]
Hey, Gene?
[GENE]
Yeah, what is it?
[JIM]
No one knows anything about
any wizards on this planet.
Never heard of 'em.
[MAN B]
Sorry.
[WOMAN A]
I'm not aware of any.
[ALL]
No wizards around here.
They've gotta be here!
Every time I went
looking for Caster shells,
people told me rumors about
these wizards who make them.
They're supposed to be on
Tenrei right here at Hagone!
[JIM] Maybe they were
messing with you.
[GENE]
Huh?!
[AISHA] Well, I can't
remember ever hearing
rumors like that
from Ctarl-Ctarl.
[GENE]
Uh?!
[SUZUKA] It's my
understanding that Casters
and their shells are the
products of a lost technology.
No one can create
them any longer.
[GENE]
Uh?!
Yeah, but what about...
...that old woman we met!
You must go to the
temple atop Mount Nantai
to find what you seek.
Ah-choo!
[GENE] I just know we'll
learn something
when we get to that temple
the old woman mentioned.
[JIM]
I dunno about that old hag.
There's somethin' fishy...
[JIM, GENE]
Ooh, wow!
[SILGRIAN giggles]
[JIM, GENE groan]
We're just wasting time now
that we have the coordinates
of the Galactic Leyline!
We should go!
Let me remind you that we're
here looking for Caster shells
because we have no idea what
to expect at the Leyline,
all right?
[AISHA] Well since we're here,
we may as well enjoy it.
[SUZUKA]
Yes, and by coincidence,
it happens to be on
the way to the Leyline.
[JIM] Fine, see if I care when
the pirates get there first.
[GENE]
Stop worrying.
Those idiots are still
screwin' around somewhere!
[MELFINA]
Um, Gene?
[GENE]
Yeah?
What exactly is a hot spring?
[GENE]
Uh?!
[JIM] Haven't you ever been to
a hot spring before, Melfina?
[MELFINA]
No, Jim.
[GENE] Well, uh... a hot
spring is a place where--
[FEMALE PA]
Attention all passengers.
As part of our customer service,
we will now fill the train
with hot natural spring water.
[TOBIGERA]
Huh?!
[TOBIGERA screaming]
Well, this is sort of
what a spring's like.
Oh!
[AISHA]
They call this hot?!
There is nothing that I
find appealing about this.
[TOBIGERA screaming]
[CONDUCTOR] Excuse me sir,
are you all right?
Sir? Sir?
Please watch out, sir.
[TOBIGERA]
Shut up!
[TOBIGERA groans]
[JIM]
Whoa! [laughing]
Whoa! Whoa!
[JIM cheering]
[GIRL A]
Ooh, what have we here?
Such an adorable little fella!
He's just my type!
Whadaya say we have
some fun with him, huh?
[JIM laughs nervously]
[GIRL C]
He's so cute!
[GIRL D] Hey sweetie pie, why
don't you come and play with us!
[AISHA]
This isn't hot! [growling]
There's nothing that I find
appealing about this.
By the way, wh-where's Gene?
[SUZUKA]
We haven't seen him.
Huh?!
You can bet it's gotta be
awfully serious then,
if that pervert isn't here.
[sneezes]
Great. I think I caught a cold.
[GENE]
Is this it?
Hm?
What the heck are those?
[buzzing]
[GENE]
Huh?!
Hey, what's goin' on here?
[ARK MANAF laughing]
[ARK MANAF]
I was just thinking
we don't get many
visitors here
in the inner temple.
And then you show up with
one of those old abominations
and red hair to boot.
[GENE]
Are you one of the wizards?
[ARK MANAF]
Wizard? I see.
Yes, perhaps that title
may be appropriate.
The old days when we once
called ourselves "priests"
are at an end.
Then can you really make
Caster shells for this thing?
I suppose.
I came here to ask you
for Caster shells.
Well, seeing as how you've
journeyed all this way...
[GENE]
Huh?
How about purchasing a souvenir?
Here's a Mount Nantai good
luck token, a lovely keepsake.
[GENE groans]
Or how about an official
Mount Nantai T-shirt
which will also bring
you good luck.
I don't care about that crap!
I just wanna know if
you're really a wizard
and if you can make
Caster shells or not?!
Hey, how dare you,
who do you think you are?!
I haven't even
announced my name yet!
I'll have you know
that I am Ark Manaf,
the twelfth head priest!
Ha!
Ah. Twelfth head priest, huh?
Yes, but that's all
in the past now.
So for the time being...
...buy something.
[GENE groans]
[TOBIGERA humming]
[ARK MANAF]
Originally, the name "Caster"
didn't refer to a gun,
but rather a wizard
who cast spells.
Long ago, this weapon
was called a Spell Gun.
Like Tao spells, the shells
seemed to have the same effect.
But do they possess magic?
[ARK MANAF]
Something caused the mana,
the mystical power of this
planet, to vanish over time.
We developed a technique of
placing spells into cartridges.
It was our attempt to
extend what little power
of the mana was left.
That was how Caster
shells came into being.
There are 20 types, each one
having a different effect.
[GENE] I've found 17
kinds of shells,
but I've never seen a
Number 4, 9, or 13.
[ARK MANAF]
Because they're rare.
A Number 9 is almost
impossible to find.
[GENE]
Oh yeah, why's that?
[HADUL]
Oh, dear me!
Ah, Lord Ark.
Is lunch ready yet?
[ARK MANAF] Only Lord Hadul
here can make a Number 9.
[HADUL]
Eh? Speak up, would you.
I can't hear very well.
[GENE]
In other words,
time has taken its toll
on the manufacturer.
Okay, so what about a
Number 4 and a Number 13?
[ARK MANAF]
I can make 13s. No problem.
But the Number 4...
[GENE]
What about 4s?
[ARK MANAF] Ah, only the
woman on Mount Nyotai.
[GENE] Oh, does that mean
I have to go there, too?
[ARK MANAF] I don't know.
I wouldn't if I were you.
Well, why not?
That damn woman!
That evil creature!
Ages ago, the three of us set
out to this planet in search of
the legendary power of mana.
It was a long, hard journey.
[GENE]
Mmm. Ya don't say?
Boy, that's interesting.
[ARK MANAF]
But instead of finding mana,
she discovered
countless hot springs.
She then ultimately transformed
this world into a
teeming tourist trap!
What's wrong with that?
[ARK MANAF]
Ahh! Plenty!
She banned men
from the summit of Mount
Nyotai, including me!
She lords over everyone,
like a queen over there!
She treats me like
I don't exist!
I haven't gotten the slightest
idea why you're so mad about.
[ARK MANAF]
Hm?
All right.
You want Caster shells,
then that means you're gonna
climb Nyotai for a
Number 4, right?
Uh... Yeah, right.
[ARK MANAF]
Take this,
and record whatever
it is Urt's up to!
And if you get any
chance at all,
shoot some dirty footage of her.
[HADUL]
Huh?! What did you say?!
Dirty footage of Urt?!
As in naked?!
[URT laughs]
[URT]
Mm...
[HADUL]
Hey! Move!
I wanna lay these
old eyes on that, too!
If you can show it to me,
I'll give you a Number
9 shell in return!
[groaning]
What is the deal with
this dirty old letch?
Ah, it's just one of his fits.
Oh, sure, climb the mountain,
bring the camera,
take some naked pictures.
I'll make you a Number 13
shell by the time you get back!
Just get me that footage!
[GENE]
Oh, brother...
[TOBIGERA panting]
[TOBIGERA grunts, yelling]
[TOBIGERA screams]
[GENE]
What was that all about?
They say that Mount Nyotai
is an unspoiled hot spring
in its natural setting, so I'm
looking forward to this.
I sure hope the water in this
one is hot for a change.
Woopee.
I'm thrilled that you guys
can just kick back and relax.
Even though I don't have
time for such luxury.
Huh?
So that's Mount Nyotai.
Now this is what makes
hot springs so appealing.
Oh, so... this is what
people find appealing
about hot springs, huh?
[SUZUKA]
Most definitely.
[AISHA]
Meow, meow, meow...
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow!
Ahh! This isn't hot!
This isn't hot at all!
Aren't there any springs around
here are hotter than this?!
I want a hot spring,
a hot spring, a hot spring!
Jim, hello?!
Can you hear me over there?
How's the water
temperature on your side?
Man, I'm really scared!
How come Gene isn't here
at a time like this?
I must be nuts.
I'm gonna freeze
to death up here.
[GENE]
No men allowed, huh?
Well, we'll just see about that!
[TOBIGERA laughs]
[shivers]
[GENE]
Huh? [screams]
What the hell...?!
[GENE groans]
[GENE, TOBIGERA groaning]
[GENE gasping]
[SILGRIAN laughs]
Ooh!
I didn't come here
for the view, lady!
[GENE] I am not gonna fall
for that trap this time.
Shit!
[SUZUKA sighs]
This is my idea of paradise.
[LADIES screams]
[MELFINA]
It's Gene!
[SUZUKA]
What's the meaning of this?!
You're in the women's bath!
[GENE]
I'm not here for the view!
[GENE mumbles, chuckles]
Get out of here you fool!
[GENE groans]
[GENE]
Okay, this time,
I am definitely not
falling for that trap!
[sighs]
[GENE chuckles]
[GENE groans]
[AISHA]
Meow, meow, meow, meow...
Now this is more like it.
[AISHA]
Huh?
[GENE]
Hot! [groaning]
[AISHA laughs]
I see...
...you came all the way
here to just to sneak a peek
at Aisha in her
birthday suit, huh?
No way, you're wrong!
I didn't come here for the--
[GENE]
Hot! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow...
It didn't take much
to get him worked up,
talk about no control.
[GENE]
All right, now I really mean it.
This time I swear...
I'm not gonna fall...
...for their damn tricks!
Ah!
[GENE groaning]
[GENE] There's no stinkin'
temple up here at the summit.
[GENE groans]
[women singing]
[GENE]
Hm?
What the...?
It sounds like women
singing down there.
[singing continues]
Oh, yeah! I'm in heaven!
I gotta get in there!
How do I get in there?!
[GENE]
All right, I'm goin' in!
I'm still here. Huh...?!
[GENE yelps]
[WOMEN scream]
[URT]
Are you awake?
[GENE]
Mm?
Hm?
Considering your gun
and the red hair,
I'll forgive the damage to the
roof and your rude intrusion.
[GENE] Then you must be the
wizard of Mount Nyotai.
[URT]
Correct.
And I am known as Urt.
Well, man with red hair,
please come with me now.
Come with you?
Why... What do you,
uh, got in mind?
[URT grunts]
[URT grunting]
[URT]
Honestly.
Ark and Hadul can
be such a bother.
[GENE] They said if
I don't bring back
some naked footage of you,
they won't give me any
Number 9 or 13 shells.
[URT]
And you?
Would you like to see
provocative images
of me as well?
[GENE]
Huh?!
[URT grunts]
[GENE grunting]
[URT]
Uh?!
[GENE]
Got it! [laughs] Yeah!
[URT]
Hm... And that's game point.
[URT] Since you won, here
they are, as I promised.
These are Number
4 cartridges.
[URT]
Hm?
Why don't we play again
and make the stakes that
risqué footage of you?
Huh?!
[URT]
And if you lose,
I get to shoot some
naughty footage of you.
It's only fair.
[GENE stutters]
I'm teasing you.
Yeah well, funny!
[URT]
Wait here for a moment.
[GENE]
Hm?
It won't take me long to
shoot some good poses.
[URT]
Hey, no peeking.
Sorry.
[ARK MANAF]
What?! Is it true?!
You actually managed
to bring back
some juicy pictures of Urt?!
[GENE] Sure did. Shot
by the lady herself.
All done. Here's the naked
footage they want.
[GENE]
It's all in here.
[BOTH laughing]
[BOTH]
Huh?!
First, the shells.
[ARK MANAF]
Here!
[HADUL]
[GENE]
That's it?!
Only one of each of 'em?
[ARK MANAF] A word of warning,
my red-headed friend.
[GENE]
Huh?
Those are very special
shells you're holding.
They're infused with a
magic that's much stronger
than any of the rest.
However, in order to activate
the shells in these times
of weak mana, a certain
catalyst is needed.
Like what? What
kind of catalyst?
You'd like to know?
I'm still waiting.
[ARK MANAF] It's the life force
of the one who fires the Caster.
[GENE]
Huh?
[HADUL]
Fire once, you'll be woozy.
Fire twice, you'll be half-dead.
So no multiple
discharges, huh?
[HADUL]
Yes, just like you know...
[GENE groans] I have more
stamina than the average man!
On to serious matters.
[HADUL]
Gimme that camera!
[GENE]
Hey!
[ARK MANAF laughs]
It's show time!
Woo-hoo!
[HADUL]
Oh, I can't wait!
Lord Ark, let's look
at it right away!
[HADUL]
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Come on!
Hey, mind if I
hang out and watch?
[ARK MANAF]
Hm.
All right, you dog! Ha, ha, ha!
So, you wanna see
a little footage?
Of... Urt... nude?
[URT laughs]
Well, let's get started!
[ALL laughing]
[URT] Just a little bit
longer... Almost there...
[ALL cheering]
Oh, you're such naughty...
...dirty... boys...
[ALL panting]
[GENE]
Man, this is great!
[HADUL]
Show us more!
[ALL cheer]
[GENE]
Hm?
Hey, what do you suppose
those numbers are for?
[HADUL] Who cares when there's
better things to look at?!
[ARK MANAF]
Oh, yeah!
[GENE]
Yeah, forget it.
[URT laughing]
Are you still watching me?
You guys really are
the biggest idiots
I think I've ever seen.
[ALL]
Huh?!
3... 2... 1... 0...
[ALL grunting]
Bitch! What an attitude!
I should've known she wouldn't
do cheesecake like that
without an ulterior motive!
[HADUL]
Ah, yes.
But it was worth it.
I saw Urt naked.
Now I can die content.
[ALL groan]
[JIM] Mister, I'll take five
bean-jam buns, please!
Hey, Gene, what the heck
took you so long, huh?
[GENE]
Just take it easy, Jim.
I managed to get the
Caster shells, didn't I?
[MALE PA]
A downhill train
will be departing
shortly on track two.
For your safety, please wait
behind the white line.
[TOBIGERA panting]
[TOBIGERA groans]
[GENE, JIM]
Wow! What was that?
[GILLIAM]
Well, it's about time.
You don't mind if I
launch now, do you?
[GENE] Right! Set a course
for the Galactic Leyline!
[ARK MANAF]
A red-haired man...
armed with a Caster gun.
[URT]
Is this a portent?
Will the universe be met
with another disaster?
[GENE] Now that we're dialed
in to the whereabouts
of the Galactic Leyline,
we gotta go there, right?
But it seems we're not the
only ones with that idea!
The pirates...
And the MacDougalls...
Looks like we'll have
a three-way struggle!
To tell ya the truth,
this looks bad!
Whenever I pilot
the Outlaw Star ,
I've gotta lead Outlaw
Star 's fat in god's hand.
What a hand job!
Next time, on Outlaw Star ,
"Cutting the Galactic Leyline"!
A warning, better prepare
yourselves for this one!