[NARRATOR]
The Toward Star World
where Gene resides
is a measureless one.
Far away from
the central areas,
four known pirate groups
vie for supremacy.
One of the four is after
the Outlaw Star and Melfina,
to destroy them.
This particular group are
pirates of the Hoppo System.
They are called the
Hundred and Eight Suns.
The most brutal member
of the Chinese Guild.
[NARRATOR]
Centered around Tendo,
the Hundred and Eight
Suns are made up
of small groups of 10 or 20.
[NARRATOR]
The leaders of these groups
control independent
organizations
and they also pursue
their own interests.
Presently, the boss
of the pirates
who is now pursuing
Gene is called Hazanko.
He has power within the
Hundred and Eight stars,
but because of the
extent of that power,
his organization and
the power of the methods
he employs to achieve his goals,
it is said that the other
leaders consider him superior.
It is also said that the squads
that carry out his orders
use a super power
called Senjutsu
and always slay those
who stand against him.
[GENE]
Are you ready Gilliam?
[GILLIAM]
Ready.
[GENE]
Let's do it.
Activating all sensor systems.
CFS... activated.
Radar... activated.
[GILLIAM]
All sensors are functioning.
Ether-drive systems...
activated.
Gravity control system...
Sub-ether drive system... set.
[GILLIAM] Navigation system
active. All systems green.
Gravity cycle unit
activated. Go.
[GILLIAM]
The Newton reactor comes first.
Uh-Oh!
[GILLIAM]
Newton reactor now activating.
Sub-reactor 1 operational...
And number two.
Number three abnormal.
What?!
[GILLIAM]
Output falling.
70... 50...
What do I do Gilliam?
[GILLIAM] Run a power balance
with the remaining reactors.
[GENE]
Oh, yeah.
[GILLIAM]
Reactors 2 and 4 output.
120... 130... 140... 160.. 180.
They are about to
explode right now.
[GENE]
Huh? What?!
[GILLIAM]
T minus 10 to critical.
10... 9... 8...
Oh, no! Gilliam.
[GILLIAM]
...6... 5... 4... 3... 2...
Another failed liftoff I see.
You're the one who
made me screw up!
Every stinkin' time
you make trouble.
[GILLIAM] Preparing for
unexpected situations
are what simulations are for.
If you are unable
to manually respond
to a small problem like this,
a liftoff is probably out of
the question for the time being.
Bite me!
[GILLIAM] Well the ship hasn't
been completely outfitted yet,
so I suppose there's no rush.
[GENE]
Oh, well...
Looks like I'd better
get back to work.
[door creaks]
[MELFINA]
Hmm?
Oh! Welcome Back!
So, anything new?
No. Not really. Ah! Oh!
What about Jim?
[MELFINA]
At the police station.
Police station?!
Yes. Apparently they
impounded Jim's car.
[GENE]
The Ehefrau?
Yes that's what he said.
[GENE]
Hm...
Well, that sort of thing doesn't
happen in Locus very often.
[MELFINA]
Huh...
I sure don't like this.
Somethin's fishy.
[horn honking]
[GENE]
Hm?
[JIM] Hey Gene!
I found her! I found her!
Hey, Gene!
Oh, she's safe and sound.
I'll never leave ya, baby.
I definitely don't like this.
[JIM] They said she'd racked
up too many parking tickets.
I tried hard to come
up with an excuse.
[GENE]
You should've just told them
that we were attacked
by pirates.
[JIM]
No way!
They never would
have believed me.
You don't even know
how much the fines
and the towing costs
added up to be.
It's crazy, I'm tellin' ya.
[footsteps]
What'll it be? Gene!
I can't believe you
two are still alive.
Yeah, it's good to
see you too, Clyde.
I heard that some
pirates were after you,
so I just assumed that, um--
[IRIS]
Gene! Thank goodness.
Iris, aw, it's okay.
[IRIS]
I've been so worried about you.
Aw, you are such a sweet heart.
Iris, you sweet thing.
I'll tell you who's
the sweet talker, you!
It's been two weeks,
what have you been up to?
It's a long boring story,
you don't wanna know.
[IRIS]
Mm! You're bad. Hm.
Oh! And who are you?
[GENE] That's Melfina.
She's a... new friend.
[IRIS]
Mm...
[CLYDE]
Iris!
[IRIS]
Uhh, yeah?!
[grunts]
Clyde, has anyone been
asking questions about us?
I mean, questions they
shouldn't be asking?
Well, after that fight, it's
been pretty busy in here.
But nobody's asked any
important questions.
[GENE]
Hmm.
I sure do not like this.
What's your problem?
[GENE]
It's nothing.
[music plays]
It seems like such a long time,
but it hasn't even been two
whole weeks since we left here.
So, now what are we gonna do?
Well, the rest of the
rest of the containers
we ordered from Fred
should be coming tomorrow.
We have to get the Outlaw Star
into perfect working order.
[JIM] Well, yeah that'd
be nice, but...
But what?
To be blunt, idiot,
we are broke!
[GENE]
Whaddya mean? The account?!
Well, yeah, there's
not much left.
The spaceport rental
took up a lotta dough.
No way! Hm.
[JIM]
One, we earn money the hard way.
But, then I wouldn't have time
to work on the Outlaw Star .
Two, we earn it the easy way.
Hey Clyde, have any big
bounties turned up lately?
No way.
Not since that time you
took down "Death" Rob.
[GENE growls]
Three, the sleazy way.
[GENE]
How?
Maybe sell your body.
Yours would sell better.
I guess three's a bust then.
[GENE]
Hmm. Four, we pay later.
Pay who?
I dunno.
[CLYDE] I don't take
credit here, you know.
--[JIM] Oh, man...
--[GENE] Oh, great.
[JIM] Well, it's gotta
be number one then.
Yeah, what about
the Outlaw Star ?
I'll leave that to you.
I'll earn us enough to live
on for the time being.
I don't know.
[MELFINA]
Um...
If there's anything I can
do to help, please tell me.
Are you good at cooking eggs?
Oh?
I'm not really sure.
I never cooked them before,
so I don't know.
Well, then you can learn now.
You're on kitchen
duty Melfina. Heh.
Um... Kay.
[GENE] Man, there's nothing
as relaxing as this town.
Yeah, yeah. Hm...
[GENE]
But.
You know, we're gonna have
to leave here pretty soon.
Yeah, I know.
But how far?
Where're we going
and just how far away.
It's nice to look up
at the sky and all, but,
let's watch where
we're stepping.
Hey, you know it'll be tough.
Yeah I know that all right.
[GENE grunting]
[GENE]
What's wrong? You can't sleep?
[MELFINA]
No.
Hey, I bet you wish bio-androids
didn't have to be so human,
is that what you're
thinkin' about, huh?
Yeah, that's right.
[GENE] Jeez, I don't understand
anything around here.
Let me stay like this
until I fall asleep.
When I'm like this,
I feel like I can dream.
I feel like I am dreaming.
[GENE]
Oh.
Hey, what do you think
you're doin' scumbag?
Oh, I, uh, I...
just thought I'd see
how human Melfina really is.
Just how human is she, hmm?
Mel's more human than you.
[GENE groans]
Hey, Jim!
Uh?
[JIM]
She's like my mom.
[sighs]
[GILLIAM] The engine covers
are not regulation parts.
So please replace them all.
Yeah, well, how about
helpin' out, huh?
[GILLIAM]
If we were in zero-G,
I would be able to
perform heavy labor,
but as you can see I am
powerless in this gravity.
Then work on the interior!
[GILLIAM]
I am of course.
Please perform a check later.
[GENE]
All right, all right.
[DOCK SUPERVISOR]
Mister Starwind!
Yeah, what?
[DOCK SUPERVISOR]
We need to talk.
Could you come to
the business office?
[sighs]
I knew this was coming.
Give me a minute, okay?
Once it comes to a boil,
reduce heat,
simmer till cooked through. Huh.
[JIM]
This thing's a goner.
I'm gonna have to
put in a new engine
or buy new parts for
just about everything!
[FARMER] If I had that kind of
money, I'd take it to a dealer.
Yes, my friend!
This is exactly when Starwind
and Hawking Enterprises
can really do it's thing.
Actually, we have an engine that
we happened to come across.
Of course, we'd charge
far less than a dealer.
[FARMER] Great! I knew it!
I knew I could count on you.
[JIM]
You bet, pal!
[DOCK SUPERVISOR]
I thought that I asked you
to pay all of the dock
fees in advance.
And if you're going to
be here for a while,
I must insist that
you pay for that too.
[GENE] We've paid you for
the next three days, right?
Well, you haven't applied
for launch clearance, I see.
We will pay you for
any overage, okay?
Just how much longer
will you be here?
I'm... not sure.
[GILLIAM] Warning!
That is not the captain...
[GILLIAM]
Gene.
Gilliam, what's goin' on?
[GILLIAM]
It's an intruder!
[door clicks]
[MELFINA]
Hey, welcome back! Huh?
[GENE]
Gilliam, where's the intruder?
[GILLIAM]
He's escaping by elevator two.
Gene! Above you!
Come here, ya jerk!
--[explosion]
--MELFINA yelps]
[MELFINA whimpers]
[MELFINA]
Oh!
[SUZUKA] I come to visit Gene
Starwind and what do I find.
Some of the most
interesting people
are trying to kill him as well.
Tell me, are you a Kei Pirate?
Don't interfere.
[SUZUKA]
Exactly what I was thinking.
Gene Starwind... is my prey.
[gasps]
Stay back now.
Uh, right!
I'll say it again.
Don't interfere with me.
Well in that case, this is
going to be a fine opportunity
to put Gene in my debt.
I finally got to
blow off some steam.
You left some lookouts
here now, didn't you?
Huh?! Am I right, Mr. Pirate?
[YASE] Heh, heh. So,
where is Hilda now?
[GENE]
Hmm?
You don't seem to understand
what you got yourself into now,
do you buddy?
[YASE]
Hmm? Is that so?
[YASE laughs]
Answer me.
Where is Hilda now?
I ain't talkin'.
[SUZUKA] Hm. So, you
are a Senjutsu Master.
You have interesting
techniques yourself.
Well, I'm just
getting warmed up.
No one has seen more than three
of my secret techniques.
You still have time;
it isn't sunset yet.
How many will you
see before dying?
You're the one that's
going to die!
[YASE yells]
[GIANT grunting]
[chanting]
Let's do it!
Hagan-raggo!
And what do you call that?
Standard Hi'en number one.
I see.
[GIANT grunting]
It's all right. It's over now.
[MELFINA]
Oh... Okay.
Do you think it would
it be all right
if I waited for
Gene in his shop?
Uh, sure.
[YASE] Looks like he's finally
dead once and for all.
Hmm.
I had questions to ask
him but it's too late.
[YASE]
What?!
[YASE screams]
[GENE]
Uh!
Damn it!
[GENE groaning]
[screams]
I have a few questions
I'd like to ask you.
Will you be a good
boy and answer?
My lucky number's one.
My very favorite color's red.
[YASE]
Where is Hilda now, huh?
Why did you and your friends
come back to Sentinel
by yourselves?
What happened to my
people? Answer me!
What'll I get?
I'll go ahead and grant
you a quick death.
You'll have to make me a
better offer than that.
Maybe I will, depending
on your answer.
[CREW A] What could have
exploded out here in the fields?
[CREW B]
I don't know!
That's why they told
us to check it out!
[gunshot]
[CREW A]
That was a gunshot.
[CREW B]
Over there!
[growls] We'll take back
the XGP! Count on it.
[CREW A]
Call for backup!
[CREW B]
Right!
[whistles]
Huh?
Any witnesses?
Nah, no one.
Apparently they're scared
of getting involved.
When it comes to pirates, I
guess I'd do the same thing.
[JIM whimpers]
Mel! What the hell
happened? Huh!
Welcome back, Jim.
What the hell are
you doin' here?
You want Gene, don'tcha?!
Yes, where is he?
Oh, yeah, like I would tell ya.
It's in your best interest
to find him soon as possible.
Because it seems
the Kei Pirates
are coming after you two.
Uh! P-Pirates?!
It's all right, don't
worry. Suzuka saved me.
[JIM]
She did?! B-But wh-why?
Because you people are
rather interesting to me. Hm.
[JIM]
Gilliam! Open up!
[GILLIAM] It's bad Jim.
There's been trouble.
We've been attacked by pirates.
Here, too? Where's Gene?
[GILLIAM]
He's inside working right now.
[JIM]
All right then, just let us in.
[GILLIAM]
Of course. Um...
Now what?
[GILLIAM]
What should we do about
that young lady you brought?
She isn't registered as a
crew member, you know.
Just let her in for
the time being.
[JIM]
Hey Gene!
Yeah, yeah, that's right,
the pirates were here.
What are we gonna do?
Well, we're gonna load up
all the equipment we can
and launch as soon as possible.
[SUZUKA]
Excuse me...
Would you please explain
what's going on here?
If you're really going to
fight the Kei Pirates,
I wouldn't mind helping
it out at all.
[JIM]
Hmm?
[GENE] At this point, all
we can do is fight them.
I don't know.
I just don't know
the real reason why.
I really have no idea.
Hey, Gene?
[GENE groaning]
Uh! Gene! What's the matter?
What's wrong?
Uh!
What? What the hell is this?
Uh. Yeah, I tried
to patched it up.
Guess I didn't do a good job.
[JIM whimpers]
[JIM]
Gene!
[GENE]
Ow!
Damn it! I'm the
star of the show.
This isn't supposed to happen...
It is just a little too
exciting, don't you think?
I'm about to go into space for
the first time with no support!
If I mess up, is the
show gonna be over?
[GENE]
Next time, on Outlaw Star :
"Forced Departure"!
You better get ready!