[NARRATOR] Gene Starwind,
Jim Hawking, Melfina,
Suzuka, Aisha Clanclan,
Fred Luo,
Ron MacDougall, Harry
MacDougall, Gwen Khan,
Hazanko, Hitoriga,
Hamuishi, Jukai, Tobigera.
The Outlaw Star , the
Geomancer , the Shangri La .
Very well then,
the cast is assembled!
I'll show you what
the Galactic Leyline is.
Well, even when you find out,
you won't be surprised.
You think you know what
it's all about, do you?
Well, maybe what
you think it is,
is only what you want it to be,
or simply something
that you want to know!
When the mystery is solved,
it's ceases to be a mystery,
and the curiosity fades with it.
Even though people know this,
they search out mysteries
because they like to say,
"Oh! So that's what it was!"
Yes. Let me start to help
you change these mysteries
you want to solve into
well known facts.
[FRED]
Gene, Jim! How are you?
Business is just fine over here.
I have both of you to thank
in more ways than one.
But I'd rather do
that in person.
That's why I keep
agreeing to your
repeated requests for
financial assistance.
But remember, as much as
I value your hard work,
the funds I send to you are
just an investment on my part.
Well, I'll be waiting
for some good news.
[JIM]
Hm. See? What did I tell ya?
Well then, I sure hope
we find treasure at
the Galactic Leyline.
Otherwise, we'll have
to skip town.
So how many shells
did you manage to get?
I have two Number 4's
and one each of Number 9
through Number 13.
But these babies here
are really important.
They can do some
serious damage.
Number 4, Number 9,
and Number 13, too!
They said not to fire
these three type shells
one right after another.
They warned me
if I do fire it,
it'll drain my life away.
Ha, ha! I doubt that!
Yeah, well I wouldn't be so
certain about that, Jim.
They said that
they're too powerful,
and will completely drain the
life out of whoever fires them.
Whoa, no way!
Gene.
Hey, come on. Don't look
at me like that.
[MELFINA]
But, Gene...
We're not gonna
get into a situation
where I have to fire
these shells back to back.
[door opens]
I'm told that the re-supply
work has been completed.
[AISHA]
Hello everyone! Sorry I'm late!
Don't worry, I took care
of all of my errands.
[GENE]
Okay, then.
Time to get this
show on the road.
The Galactic Leyline's
waiting for us.
Tell me Harry, how do you feel?
[HARRY]
I'm feeling fine.
I can pretty much make the
ship do whatever I want.
And that's not all
of it, I assure you.
Mm... Not at all.
If I'm not mistaken Harry,
you should be able to navigate
your way to the
Galactic Leyline,
without a hitch, just like
your friend Melfina.
Don't worry.
[HARRY] I like it when you
compare me to her, Professor.
Remember now Khan,
let's keep focused on
our true mission here,
I didn't go through the
trouble of tracking you down
just to save Harry.
Yes, I know that.
I never would have
helped out you two
if I hadn't been humiliated
and abandoned by those people.
They'll pay for the
disrespectful way
I've been treated,
I can assure you.
Well then, it seems as if
we have a common interest.
Yes, that's quite right!
It appears my tracer
aboard the Outlaw Star
is operating perfectly so far.
If we follow them, we'll arrive
at the Galactic Leyline!
[FRED]
Wait for me, Melfina.
[OLD MAN, OLD WOMAN chanting]
[HAZANKO]
Continue.
[OLD MAN, OLD WOMAN chanting]
[OVERSEER]
Hazanko!
What is the meaning of this?
You're not following the orders
of the Tendo King as commanded.
[HAZANKO]
I most certainly am.
As ordered, I have
through my own means,
found a way into the Leyline.
And I've done so without
breaking any laws.
So then, why haven't you
reported your progress
to the Tendo King?
Why are you not opening
the Leyline on your own?
[HAZANKO]
What's the matter,
doesn't the Tendo King
sycophant have any ambitions?
It's just as I thought, Hazanko!
What you really have in
mind is to betray the king
and take the Leyline for
yourself! That's it, isn't it?
[HAZANKO]
Not just the Tendo King.
The power of the Galactic
Leyline surpasses
that of the Tenpa Emperor.
No, it's magnificent power
is even greater than that!
[OVERSEER]
Die!
Damn you, Hazan... ko...!
[HAZANKO]
Let's finish this.
[HAZANKO] When the
Overseer doesn't return,
the Tendo King will
grow suspicious.
Before then, I'll have
in my possession
everything the
Leyline has to offer!
[beeping]
A ship has appeared
out of sub-ether space.
It's heading straight
for the Galactic Leyline.
[HAMU]
Oh, no, it can't be!
[HAZANKO]
The XGP!
[GILLIAM]
That area of space is odd.
Electromagnetic waves,
gravity waves, ether waves.
Nothing I send out comes back.
Are you saying it doesn't
come up on your sensors?
[GILLIAM]
That's right.
A malfunction when the
Leyline's under our noses?
[GILLIAM] My sensors are
functioning normally.
I'm picking up other ships
along that area's periphery.
You're picking up ships?!
Why didn't you say so?
[GILLIAM]
I'll magnify the image for you.
Those are Kei Pirates!
They're all over the place!
[GENE]
An ambush!
[SUZUKA] There seems to
be many worker ships.
That looks like...
the Geomancer !
Wait, you know that ship?
It's the ship of a man named
Hazanko who is said to be
a powerful Tao master,
even among the Kei leaders.
Hazanko?
He's a dangerous man.
And with him, the Anten
Pirates, his subordinates.
Are you talking about that
bunch that attacked us?
[beeping]
[GILLIAM] Pirate ships are
launching cub fighters!
Count: many!
All right. Prepare for combat!
[HAZANKO]
I want you to capture the XGP.
And then, take Melfina!
Take that!
They're trying to keep us away
from the Galactic Leyline!
[MELFINA] A ship is coming
out of sub-ether space.
Seven hundred kilometers
to starboard.
Reinforcements?!
[GILLIAM]
Now enlarging.
Look at that...
We got a trouble.
Wait a minute,
Gene, isn't that...?
It's the entire
Ctarl-Ctarl Empire's
Deep Space Fleet vessel!
The Nipopopolas-class cruiser,
the Orta Honehone !
[XO] The Ctarl-Ctarl
Empire will lay claim
to the Galactic Leyline!
Smash anyone who dares
to get in our way!
Gagagan Cannons! Fire!
Aisha? What the hell
have you done?
Every time we went
to a spaceport,
I always contacted
the empire, that's all.
What?
You gave them the
Leyline's coordinates?
If I don't let them know where
I'm going and what I'm doing,
my family and friends
get worried sick about me.
[HAMU] The Ctarl-Ctarl warship
seems to be heading straight
for the Galactic Leyline.
[HAZANKO] Let them do
whatever pleases them.
We wouldn't have had to
go through all this trouble
if it were possible to force
your way into the Leyline.
[CTARL CREW]
Go! Go!
Nothing can stop the
invincible Ctarl-Ctarl!
Nothing can stop
the Ctarl-Ctarl.
Go! Go! Ctarl-Ctarl!
We're not afraid of anything!
We're the invincible
Ctarl-Ctarl!
They did it!
This means that
the entire treasure
belongs to the
Ctarl-Ctarl Empire!
Ah, damn it!
Haven't you ever heard of
the expression "fair play"?
No use getting upset over it.
Bastard!
Whaddaya think that
you're the only one
that's in a race to
get to the Leyline?
[HAMU] The XGP is a
formidable opponent.
[OLD MAN]
Huh?
Oh...
[HAZANKO]
What is it?
They are coming this way.
[CTARL CREW screaming]
[gasps] Is that the
Orta Honehone ?
Why's it coming back this way?!
Look at their shots.
They're firing at random.
Turn to 3 o'clock.
And do it now!
[GILLIAM]
That's crazy!
The Orta Honehone would
be directly in our path!
That is our only shot at
making it to the Leyline!
[MELFINA] We'll never be
able to dodge them all!
Position shield to
maximum protection!
[JIM, AISHA scream]
All right, we're goin' in!
We really did it, Gene!
It's a straight shot in
to the Leyline from here.
[GILLIAM] It's not registering
on my sensors.
I'm afraid there
doesn't appear to be
anything at all
that I can detect.
Melfina!
[MELFINA] Turn control of
the Outlaw Star over to me.
It seems the XGP
has successfully
penetrated the Leyline.
I'm detecting a new ship.
[HAMU]
Receiving transmission.
Well, well, if it isn't Hazanko.
What an unexpected pleasure,
meeting you in this
godforsaken place.
[HAZANKO]
Ronald MacDougall?
What are you doing here?
I'm letting the XGP lead
me to the Galactic Leyline.
And you'd better guess again if
you think you're gonna stop me!
[HAZANKO]
What do you think you're up to?
Loathsome jackals like you
don't have a chance in
hell of getting in there.
Jackals, huh?
No, we're the big game hunters.
We're gonna take down
the XGP for openers,
then plunder the Leyline.
Yes, you heard right!
The knowledge of the
universe will be mine.
[HAZANKO]
Gwen Khan!
[GILLIAM] None of my sensors are
picking up anything unusual.
I have no idea what
is around the ship.
[GENE]
What is the ship's status?
[GILLIAM]
All green.
[AISHA]
What...?
Uh-oh, what's that noise?
D'ya hear that?
[GILLIAM]
Noise? What noise is that?
I am not detecting
anything at all.
[screaming]
Oh, my head's
gonna split open!
Mel, what's goin' on?
[MELFINA]
Wait. Just wait.
[GILLIAM]
Hold on.
Hold on, everyone!
[HAMU] The Shangri-la
is entering the Leyline.
[HAZANKO] I cannot believe
that Gwen Khan is with them.
Well, old man?
There's just one
that still remains.
[GILLIAM]
I can't sense anything.
Nothing at all!
[ALL screaming]
[MELFINA]
This is the spiral.
[MELFINA] I've adjusted
the ship's orientation.
This will take us there.
Melfina?
[MELFINA] This will take us
to the center of the Leyline.
What's that noise?
It's driving me insane!
What's happening? Can't
anybody make it go away?!
Harry!
[HARRY]
Everything's okay, Ron.
I can see the path.
It's getting clear.
And I can see her
at the end of it!
[chanting]
[ALL gasping]
[screaming]
It... It's opening.
[HAZANKO] We're now entering
the Galactic Leyline!
Melfina, what's our status?
[MELFINA]
Engine output: 70 percent.
We're following a spiral
course that will send us
directly into the center.
We wouldn't be able to tell
where we're going
without you, Mel.
Yeah, you said it!
[AISHA]
Hmm.
I guess it looks like
the Orto Honehone
wasn't up to the challenge.
So that must be the reason why
the Geomancer held its position.
What were they doing,
just standing by like that?
Who knows, Jim.
But I'll betcha they're cooking
up some dirty little scheme,
and we'll be ready for them.
Oh, my!
It seems like I can't pick
up my tracer, either!
[HARRY] Don't worry,
I know where they are.
They're just ahead of us.
We'll meet up with them soon.
She's all mine now!
Now, now, son!
You're underestimating
the trouble
you'd have mating with her. Hm.
I wonder what would happen?
[HARRY]
It's okay, professor,
I already know that
she's a bio-android.
You think she's a bio-android?
No, no.
She's a considerably different
from the standard issue
bio-androids that we've
become familiar with.
Different in ways that
you can't imagine.
[HARRY]
Yeah, so how's she different?
[KHAN]
Mm-hm...
I'll need to start
at the beginning.
You see, the Kei
Pirates came to me
and asked me to decode
genetic engineering data
uncovered by them
at some ancient ruins
called "Grave of Dragon."
I already know how you designed
the XGP after decoding the data,
professor, just stick
to Melfina.
But that's just it.
You see, I wasn't able
to completely decode it.
Some of the data I mentioned
was something even I couldn't
precisely understand.
For lack of a better term,
I have been calling
it a "black box."
The XGP, as well as Melfina,
were constructed by
incorporating this "black
box," which I had no idea
how to activate, as
well as knowledge from
30,000 years ago,
left behind by a
mysterious source.
Yes.
So you're saying that hidden
inside the XGP and Melfina
lies a mystery you could
never solve, professor?
Yes, yes, yes, that's right!
Oh, how can there still be
so many unsolved mysteries
of the universe that my
brilliant mind can't decipher?
It's utterly
impossible to fathom!
At any rate, there's your
answer in a nutshell.
She's too great a mystery
for you to contemplate.
[HARRY]
I can sense them!
At last I've found you, Melfina!
Turn the ship around! Damn it!
It's the MacDougall brothers!
What are they doin' here?!
Melfina?
[MELFINA]
The spiral's collapsing.
What just happened there?!
[MELFINA]
I think it's a whirlpool?!
I'm detecting another ship!
It's the Geomancer .
[HAZANKO]
Capture the XGP at once!
Then destroy the
MacDougall brothers!
[HARRY]
Don't mess with me!
Don't try to fight them
head-on! Go after the XGP!
All right, bastard!
Dammit!
--Gene!
You moron!
[HARRY] You think I'm gonna let
you have Melfina that easily?
Let's lose 'em.
Maximum overdrive.
After them!
[HARRY]
I know!
[HAZANKO] Don't let them
escape! After them!
[OLD MAN] With all due respect,
we musn't, Lord Hazanko.
If we deviate from our course,
we'll never stand a chance
of reaching the Leyline.
[GENE]
Mel!
Where's that spiral?
[MELFINA]
We're in the center.
[GILLIAM]
Kinetic waves.
There's something ahead.
Wha...? What's that?
Wha? That's it, isn't it?!
That's what the Kei Pirates
have been trying to mastermind.
It's where mountains of riches
are waiting for all of us!
So that's it.
The heart of the
Galactic Leyline!
Whadddaya think
we'll find there?
Treasures or monsters?
Let's find out. [grunts]
[MELFINA]
The ship is being pulled in.
It's like we're being guided.
Guided?
Don't you think that's
a little understated?
Oh, no! We're gonna crash!
[GILLIAM] Acceleration has
dropped to approximately 70%.
I'm detecting an atmosphere
outside the ship.
So, Gene, what are
we gonna do now?!
Show some backbone, will ya?
The Leyline is sending
us an invitation.
I say we accept the offer.
Looks like the end of the line.
[GILLIAM]
Oh my goodness.
Huh?
[GILLIAM]
Take a look at this, Gene.
It seems to be some sort
of artificial structure.
[GENE] So the rest of
the way is by foot, huh?
[GILLIAM] The atmosphere
is quite breathable.
The gravity is
approximately 0.974 G.
Man, these guys think
of everything, don't they?
Mind the ship while
I'm gone, Gilliam.
[GILLIAM] All right,
I'll see you later, then.
Please be careful.
[HAZANKO]
Tobigera, you and the crew
will protect the Geomancer .
[TOBIGERA]
Yes, sir!
[HAZANKO]The rest of you
will come with me!
[ALL]
Yes, lord!
Well, what do you think, Harry?
How does your body feel?
[HARRY sighs]
It feels great!
I'm lighter on my feet
than I was in my real body.
[KHAN] Yes, it's certainly
powerful, all right,
but remember that body is
your life support system.
[HARRY]
Yes, I understand.
[JIM] Man, this place really
gives me the creeps!
[GENE]
Oh...
Looks like a dead end!
Okay, Gene, what
should we do now?
Like we have a choice.
We gotta go back.
Hey, what's with the
bright lights?! Man!
It's gone!
What the...?!
[JIM]
What is this?
[AISHA]
The cave's disappeared!
It's like we've been
transported to another place.
[JIM]
What's going on, Gene?
[GENE]
How in the world should I know?
It seems to me that we're
inside the cylinder now.
Don't you know what's
going on, Melfina?
[MELFINA]
Huh?
No, I don't know, either.
I'm confused, too.
[AISHA]
You are?
[MELFINA]
I don't even know how I did it!
I don't understand
why I was able
to guide the Outlaw Star here.
This was the first time
I could do it. [cries]
Well, we traveled all this way
so we could find that out.
[HAZANKO]
Shall I tell you all, then?
[ALL]
Huh?
Who are you?
[HAZANKO]
Heh. It's because Melfina
has had the secret
of the Leyline
within her all this time.
That's Hazanko and they're...
Yeah I know, those Anten guys.
[HAZANKO]
You will return Melfina to me.
She belongs to us now!
Melfina isn't a
poker chip, Jack.
Forget it!
[KHAN]
Oh my, my, my, my, my!
How amazing!
Was that teleportation?
[GENE]
MacDougall!
Yeah, and why is
Gwen Khan with those guys?
[VOICE]
Why dost thou return?
Hey, what was that?!
[VOICE]
Why dost thou return?
I don't understand.
What does she mean
I've returned?
Melfina!
[VOICE]
What is thy desire?
What do you want?!
[VOICE]
What is thy desire?
[HAMU]
That voice.... who is it?
[VOICE] Find thy desire
here on this land.
[KHAN]
Oh...
Yeah, I got your desire!
[screams]
[VOICE]
Why dost thou return?
Whom dost thou guide?
[GENE] Melfina, I never
knew anything about you.
And now that you're gone,
I realize that I need you.
Here at the Galactic Leyline,
I'll find something
and I'll lose something.
Wait for me.
[GENE]
Be there!
Next time, on Outlaw Star :
"Maze of Despair"!
You better get ready!