[NARRATOR]
It was the brain
of ether physicist
Dr. Sam Kaseinpow,
the Chosong Science
Company's Technology Group
that was led by
Professor Hata Ikkei.
The donation of enormous
amounts of capital
made by every country,
and above all, Dragonite,
that made the Munchhausen
Drive a reality.
In year 1 of the
Toward Stars calendar,
an unknown crystalline
material, Dragonite,
was discovered in a meteorite
that crashed in the Arashan
Desert in northern China.
It was found to be a catalyst
that released tremendous
amounts of energy
from the inexhaustible ether.
In search of Dragonite,
humanity stampeded into space.
It could be considered the
gold rush of the Space Age.
But Dragonite was an
extremely rare substance
in the vastness of space.
An alchemical method of
synthesizing it artificially
is being researched
at this time,
but has yet to be perfected.
As a non-renewable resource,
Dragonite is highly valued,
and is considered
to be the rarest,
most valuable substance
in the universe.
Uh-huh! That sure smells good!
Uh?
Hey, part-timer! What're you
doing just standin' around?!
Take it to that table!
Yes, sir!
Sorry for the wait.
Huh?
[screams]
Y-Y-Y-You guys! W-W-Why?!
--[JIM] Uhh...
--[GENE] Huh?
Uh. Hi, Aisha.
What are the hell
you doing here?!
How can you order this
kind of fancy food?!
And where did you get
that kinda money?
A customer's payin' for it.
We're just s'pposed
to wait here for him.
This guy happens to be
a real generous client.
He said we could have
anything we wanted
while we're just waitin'
around for him.
--[JIM] Mmm...
--[GENE] This is great!
Yeah, it's really rich,
but it doesn't have
that yucky aftertaste
you usually get with
this kind of food, huh?
Uh. Oh, yes. He's right.
[growling]
Huh?
If you want, you can have
some of my lobster.
Ahh...
Don't mind if I do!
--Thanks! Ugh!
--[OWNER] Hey, part-timer!
[OWNER] Stop screwin' around!
Get your butt back here!
[AISHA]
Ugh! Yes, sir.
[GENE]
Hm?
Looks like our client
finally showed up.
[JIM, MELFINA]
Huh?
[JIM]
So, what can we do for ya?
On the phone you said you
were looking for something,
so what might that be, hm?
I'm lookin' for a treasure.
Huh? Wha--?
Did he say what I think he said?
Actually, we don't have to look
far. I already know where it is.
The ship with the treasure
went down on a certain planet.
All I need for you to do
is bring it back up for me.
A salvage operation?
I'm sorry, but with
our equipment,
I'm afraid that'd be a
little difficult for us.
With a Grappler Ship,
it won't be a problem.
I've already had a chance to see
you're ship at the spaceport.
She's a perfect vessel.
Yeah, well, Gilliam would
sure be happy to hear that.
But what do you need
a Grappler Ship for?
The environment on that
planet is sort of special.
A Grappler Ship would
be best suited for it.
What do you mean by "special"?
I can't tell ya
anymore right now.
And what about the treasure?
[OLD MAN] Something worth
at least five million wong.
Five? Five million?
In what? Jewels?
Hey! I said that I can't
tell you anymore.
It depends now on the
answer you give me.
[JIM]
Hmm...
Uh... We'll be just one minute.
What should we do?
There's something
fishy about all of this.
You can tell that there's
something going on
just by looking
at that old geezer.
That's for sure.
A treasure hunt with that
old man running the show?
I normally wouldn't be
interested in this sort of thing
but...
Even if it's only half
of that, it's still 2.5.
We'd make a killing!
[GENE] But backing
that old man? I don't know.
[JIM] No kidding.
That's the tough part,
but the money's good.
[GENE] I'm not sure.
It still seems kinda fishy.
Yeah, but come on, Gene,
we're totally broke.
We don't have much of
a choice in the matter.
Necessity's the mother
of an invention.
So what do you say?
Should we go for all or nothin'?
I just hope we get
rich quick. You gotta deal.
[JIM clears throat]
Sorry that look so long.
After careful deliberation,
we've decided to
accept your job offer.
Starwind and Hawking
at your service, sir.
Uh, uh...
Just call me Old Man.
--[JIM] What?
--[GENE] Uhh...
Being called "Sir" sounds
like empty flattery.
Call me "Gramps" or "Old Man,"
whichever you like.
[JIM]
Umm...
I'm not the least bit surprised
that you don't trust me.
I have to admit this
story is pretty fishy.
Uh, well... that is...
[OLD MAN laughing]
It's all right. Somebody
with a one-track mind
who would take
the job right away
would never be
able to handle it!
But I also wouldn't
team up with somebody
who doesn't have the guts
to go chasin' after a dream.
And you people pass.
[groans]
I'm honored then.
[chukles] I like that
look in your eye.
Huh?
[OLD MAN]
Those are the eyes of an Outlaw
who'd go anywhere
to chase his dreams.
Heh!
[gasps]
[ALL]
Huh?
[THUG A]
Die, Old Man!
[THUG B]
This is for our brother!
All right, come
outta there, Old Man!
Kinda looks as though the
only thing they're after
is that old man.
Here.
Hey, it doesn't matter to me.
Anyone who shoots in
my direction is an enemy.
Ahh, it's ridiculous.
No one wastes food
right in front of me
and gets away with it!
[screaming]
--[AISHA screaming]
--[THUGS groaning]
When Aisha gets like that,
she's totally outta control.
Well shootin' your gun off
didn't help, you know. Gah!
I wonder who those
people were anyway.
[OLD MAN] Some of the people
who are tryin' to kill me.
[JIM]
Huh?
When did you get here?!
I didn't have a
chance to tell you,
but there're people who're after
information about the treasure
that have been trailing
me for some time now.
[GENE, JIM, MELFINA, groan]
Well, then, I suppose
that makes my story real.
[JIM]
Hm?
[chuckling]
[growling]
What are you tryin' to do,
put me out of business?!
[AISHA]
Hm? Ah!
[OWNER crying]
You, the boy, and the little
lady, are you the whole crew?
Just the three of you?
Well sometimes we team up
with two of the others
when we need the
help, but yeah,
basically we are the crew.
But I can handle most
of the problems myself.
[OLD MAN sighs]
That's really too bad.
Physical strength's important
on the last leg of the trip.
[AISHA]
Okay, Gene Starwind.
You're gonna pay for the
damage to the restaurant,
do you understand?!
[GENE]
Uh...
Aisha, you're just in time!
If it's strength you want,
this animal here has got
the strength of ten!
[ASHIA]
Nya?
Who are you calling an animal?!
Establishing all
navigation data.
[MELFINA] Output of all
engines is stable.
We can launch.
Okay, so where are
we headed, Old Man?
Heifong VII, the Water Planet!
All right, let's go!
I've come back! I've come
back again! Finally!
Gramps, whaddya
mean when you say
you've come back again?
I didn't wanna say anything,
but I've had my fill of comin'
back here many times before
over the past 30 years.
What? Did you say 30 years?
What's this?
Our entry course to
the Water Planet
to supply you with the data.
All right! Yes, sir!
Way cool!
They don't call it the Water
Planet for nothing, do they?
It's more like we're in
water instead of gas.
[GILLIAM] The pressure of the
planet is compressing the gas
into a liquid.
It is like being in an
ocean of hydrogen.
Cut your engines now.
Go to silent running.
Why do you wanna do that?
[OLD MAN]
Do as I say.
Mel, go ahead. Set engine
systems to waiting mode.
[MELFINA]
Understood.
Now setting Ether Drive System
and Sub-ether Drive System
to waiting mode.
Now pitch us down
three more degrees.
Roger that!
Hey, look at the fish!
Wow! I can't believe there's
fish in a place like this.
They look tasty!
[screams]
Wh-What's that?
That thing is huge!
A demon.
A demon?
The same demon that dwells
in the Water Planet.
What do ya mean by demon?
And what else have you decided
not to tell us, Old Man?
No more secrets now.
Just tell us everything.
Okay, I'll tell you everything.
For starters, how 'bout the
explosives in this prosthetic?
Explosives?
[OLD MAN chuckles]
I'm used to being betrayed.
This arm is loaded with enough
to blow this ship sky-high
if need be.
Heh. Do you really think
that I'm stupid enough
to fall for a bluff like that?
Do you wanna find out?
See if I'm bluffing?
[JIM]
Uh... No.
All right, then.
About 30 years ago,
a ship run by pirates
had been brutally
attacked by an Outlaw family
where it crashed here
on the Water Planet
and was left behind.
Along with her cargo
of 15 tons of Dragonite.
Fifteen tons of Dragonite?
[GILLIAM] That equals the state
budget of the frontier world
for a total of five years.
Then the Outlaws came after it.
They chased right
after that pirate ship
as she sank into the gas ocean.
And when the pirate ship reached
the sea of metallic hydrogen,
invading the
unknown territory...
...that's when those
monsters appeared.
The monsters had floated up
from the bottom of the sea
and attacked the Outlaw ships.
Their claws ripped
through the armor plating
and their fangs crushed
through their hulls!
The monsters that slaughtered
12 of the family's ships
in an instant were a pack
of primitive life forms
that have made the
Water Planet their home.
Whoa! Wait a minute, Gramps!
That monster we saw
was part of a pack?
The area the pirate
ship went down in
was somewhere near their colony.
They have a strong
territorial instinct.
Anything that invades their
territory is attacked.
Without any mercy,
Outlaws, Pirates, Space Forces,
anyone seeking the treasure
has been shredded by
their relentless claws
and sent straight
to the bottom.
The Water Planet came
to be known as the place
where the evil demon lives.
Fear kept people
from coming back.
They no longer searched
for the treasure.
[GENE]
But that's not true for you.
After meeting the
demon 30 years ago,
you're the only one now
who's still chasing
after the treasure.
I find that kind of interesting.
Huh? What're ya talking about?
I'm taking a guess
that it was your family
that attacked the pirate ship.
Am I right?
Yeah?
I've lost many things
in my lifetime.
My eye, my leg,
of course, and my hand.
My family is irreplaceable.
They took them away from me!
For 30 years I've kept hunting!
The monster! The treasure!
And I won't stop
until I get them!
For revenge?
No! It's the only way
an Outlaw lives!
I have a dream to chase after.
I have an enemy to kill.
So I will keep
fighting as long I can.
I'll keep fighting as
long as I'm an Outlaw.
[beeping]
[MELFINA]
I see something ahead.
That's the vessel!
So your tellin' me
15 tons of Dragonite
are waiting inside
of that thing?
Uhh... Let's get
outta here, Gene!
This place is crawling
with monsters
that can crush a spaceship and
chew us up like tiny morsels.
[GENE]
You have a plan, right?
[OLD MAN]
Of course!
Tell me you're not gonna do it!
Do you really think
I'm gonna turn around
and run with 15 tons
of Dragonite out there?
We're gonna get the treasure
that's been sitting here
for 30 years and
take it with us.
Aw, come on, Gene!
[GENE]
Pull yourself together, Jim!
This is our big chance
to make a quick fortune.
I cannot believe this.
Okay, fine.
Okay, Old Man.
What do we do first?
Ready some decoys right away.
[sighs] Roger!
Decoy loading complete!
Fire 'em straight at
the pirate ship now!
[AISHA]
Nya?
They sound just like those
fish we saw earlier.
You mean to tell me
that you can hear that?
Of course I can!
Evade!
Got it!
Go ahea! Cut the wires!
Set engines to maximum!
Aye-aye, sir!
All right, it worked!
Hey, this is a lot
easier than I thought!
Don't get cocky.
We only have ten minutes
before they come back
to their territory.
That should give us just
enough time to board the ship
so we can load up the treasure.
[OLD MAN]
It's in cargo hold three.
Right, I gotcha!
Careful, Old Man.
I wouldn't want ya to have
a heart attack or anything.
You could be rest assured
I'm not gonna die
till I get my hands
on that treasure!
[OLD MAN]
Damn! It won't open!
[GENE]
Stand back!
Okay, then! It's time
for Aisha to get to work!
And that's the way
we take care of that!
[AISHA]
Hey! What's the big--? Uh!
Hey, you guys, I-- Ah!
[AISHA]
Nya! This is all Dragonite!
It's been so long.
The day has finally arrived.
[crying]
Sorry, Old Man, but we
don't have time for this.
You can be overcome with emotion
after we've loaded
up the treasure.
Oh yeah, right.
[MELFINA]
Will they make it?
All we can do now is hope
that what the Old Man
told us is true.
Gene, you only have
three minutes left!
I gotcha, Jim.
This is the last of it.
What the hell just happened?!
[JIM] It's the monsters! They're
back! They're everywhere!
What?!
This isn't what you told us!
I'm sorry, it looks like
I miscalculated.
You miscalculated?!
[JIM]
What should we do, Gene?
Hang on, Jim, till we get back!
[GILLIAM]
Ugh! My hull is being damaged!
What're you doing, Jim?
Fight back with the Grappler
Arms before it's too late!
Calm down, okay?
We can't use the Grappler Arms
until we've rescued Gene
and all of the others.
All right, Jim! We've got
the treasure all loaded!
You can pull us in now!
Okay!
Disengage waiting mode!
Get us outta here, full thrust!
[MELFINA]
Roger!
Output of all
engines is stable.
What the hell was that?!
[GILLIAM] Apparently the left
arm is weighted down.
What's that?!
You think you can take us?
Damn! That thing is powerful!
Yeah, and he's huge!
[OLD MAN]
It's the master!
Yeah, that's the one.
The demon among demons
that took my life
and shattered it
to hell and back!
The demon king
of the Water Planet.
Demon King of the Water Planet?
[GENE] Mel! Fire up the
engines immediately!
[gasps]
Take it to full power
and break free.
It's not working! It's using
the pirate ship as leverage.
It's clamped down too tight!
The arms are not gonna hold!
Shit! If this keeps up,
we're dead. Gah, come on!
[gasps]
[MELFINA]
The cargo hatch is opening.
[GENE]
Say what?!
Old Man, what the hell do
you think you're doing now?
[OLD MAN] Heh. Settle things
with that villainous bastard.
[GENE]
Settle things?! Don't be stupid!
What do you think you
can possibly accomplish
in that mini-sub?
Thanks to you people, I was
able to fulfill my dream
in more ways than one.
I spent all my years as an
Outlaw chasin' after this.
A beautiful dream that
has now come to life!
[GENE]
Old Man...
[OLD MAN]
All that's left now is him.
He's right in front of me,
and the Outlaw honor
says I have to kill it!
[GENE]
Old Man! Don't!
There's still time!
Don't do it! Just let go!
Stop!
Don't do it!
[gasps]
[OLD MAN] You must search for
your own dream, young Outlaw!
And then fight for it!
Fight to make it all yours!
Come on! Please, don't do it!
Old Man!
[AISHA]
We did it! We did it!
We have a mountain of treasure!
--[beep]
--[JIM groans]
Well? Well?
So how much did we make
and what's my cut?
[JIM]
Zero!
[AISHA]
Huh?!
What do you mean zero?
With all that Dragonite?!
You gotta be crazy!
You tryin' to pull
one over on me?!
It may look like a lot,
but it's low density.
On the black market, it only
comes to 1.8 million wong.
Take a look for yourself.
Here's the fuel bill, the cost
of fixing the Grappler Arms,
the cost of replacing
the armor plating.
And all this is the
maintenance of the ship.
Parking fees and rent for
the office keep piling up.
There's utilities,
phone, advertising,
plus the incidentals,
and we're left with this!
[wailing]
Is it true?
Why is this happening to me?!
[GENE] The secret of the Outlaw
is finally revealed!
And MacDougall tries to get
Melfina into his slimy clutches!
Yeah!
This feels like we're
moving in on the climax
of a great space drama,
doesn't it?
Not exactly.
But what's real exciting
is next week, I'm gonna
have to pilot a giant robot!
Huh? I'm not?
Well let's hope the
robot isn't piloting me!
Next time on Outlaw Star :
"Between Life and Machine"!
You better get ready!