[NARRATOR] With the development
of the Munchhausen Drive,
which made faster-than-light
space travel possible,
humanity entered into a
new era of great odysseys.
They set out into the universe,
into this infinite sea.
Explorers, soldiers,
colonists...
...all sorts of travelers
with all sorts of names,
crossed the sea of
stars and spread out
across all sorts of worlds.
But when law and
order were created,
those who disturbed it,
appeared.
And when wealth and
interest were made,
those who would plunder
them, appeared.
Just as in the last
great age of sailing,
pirates were
reborn in space.
But in this new
age of odysseys,
a new breed of sailors appeared
who worked outside the law, yet,
sided with neither space
pirate nor Space Forces.
Outlaws.
This was the name given to
those who traveled space
with only his freedom
as his guide.
Well, well, well, here he is.
You have gotta be kiddin' me.
Hold it!
Hey! Don't worry.
[GENE]
They're just paint bullets.
But, not normal ones, heh.
[OUTLAW A groaning]
[laughs]
That won't take it off!
Ya can't see a damn
thing, can ya?!
[OUTLAW A]
You asked for it, kid!
Better say your prayers!
Damn kid.
All right!
I'll getcha, now!
[laughs]
[OUTLAW A]
You're history, that's it!
You're all mine!
[screaming]
[groans]
Huh?
So, you've got a lot of tricks
up your sleeve, I see.
Hey, I don't think these
guys were after you
just because of what
you did back at the bar.
Well, looks like...
...just about everybody's
after you.
[thud, groaning]
Okay, so tell me, what the
hell do you want with me?
[groaning]
I don't know, I tell ya...!
Com'on, I don't know anything!
But you know my
reputation, right?
[OUTLAW B]
Uh... Someone asked us to do it!
They told us we
could capture you
or we could just keep you here!
Gonna tell me who?
Somebody even worse than me?
[gasps]
[sighs] It's Ron MacDougall.
MacDougall?
Why him?
I don't know, we just did it.
Cause he offered to
pay us a lot of money.
[HILDA]
I see...
[OUTLAW B groaning]
[HILDA]
Wake up Melfina and Jim.
We're going to the dock.
So, who's this MacDougall guy?
[HILDA]
I'll explain later.
[GENE]
Hmm... I've heard that before.
[MIKEY]
Okay!
That's the last of 'em.
[SWANZO] Looks like you guys
made it here in one piece.
[HILDA]
Sorry about the trouble.
[SWANZO chuckles]
Don't mention it.
We go back a long way.
I wouldn't mind knowing what
they were up to, though.
Looks like MacDougall
put them up to it.
Oh! So, he's goin' all-out, huh?
What have you got
yourself mixed up in?
Well, it's nothing major.
It's the Galactic Leyline.
[SWANZO]
The Galactic Leyline?!
I'll never understand
how you Terans think.
You really believe
in that stuff?
Actually, no, Swanzo,
I don't believe anything
until I see it with my own eyes.
How's Horus, doing?
[SWANZO]
I've finished with the supplies.
How are the engines, Mikey?
[MIKEY]
All green.
Except, you've got less than 50
parsecs left until your next
recommended overhaul on
your Sub-ether Drive.
The manufacturer's too paranoid.
We're launching right away.
[GENE]
Hey hold it!
You mean we're just gonna
launch now, just like that?
[SWANZO]
That's probably a good idea.
There's a big ruckus
over at Dock 12.
Maybe their buddies are
sending out some ships.
[GENE growls]
What, are you out of your mind?
Starting a fight right
outside Blue Heaven?
[SWANZO]
They're breaking the rules
if they don't go hand-to-hand.
And Horus is too big for them.
It's like [gibberish]
[GENE]
Hm?! Whadchu just say?
[SWANZO]
Uh. Sorry, translator glitch.
I mean, "Sharks ganging
up on a whale."
Ha! Whatever.
I've never even seen
a whale before.
[HILDA]
Swanzo,
thank you for everything, I'll
be back soon and understand,
I will need your help again.
I'll have a new ship with me...
[SWANZO]
No problem, Hilda.
[HILDA]
Okay, let's get going!
[HORUS] Five class-C Grappler
Ships have launched
from Blue Heaven
and are closing in.
Gene!
Hey, Gene!
Huh? What is it?
[HILDA] You ever fought
in a space ship before?
No. Even if I did,
I don't want to now.
I thought you had some
experience as a pilot.
[GENE]
I do!
But I might puke
all over the console.
[HORUS]
Warning.
That may cause a short-circuit.
If you don't have a problem
with it, I'll help.
[HILDA]
Can you operate a laser cannon?
Sure, I know how to use one.
[HILDA]
It's to your right.
If they close in, open fire!
[JIM]
Okay!
[GENE]
Uh?
[grunts]
[HILDA]
Melfina!
[gasps] Huh?
Sit in the auxiliary
control chair.
You're able to do it.
All right. I'll try.
[HORUS]
Warning.
Please avoid any reckless
evasive maneuvers
until we are out of Blue
Heaven's approach lanes.
All right, continue
accelerating.
They won't get away!
Let's split ourselves up!
[RADIO OUTLAW]
Right!
Those bastards messed with us,
and now it's time
for some payback!
[HORUS] Grappler Ships to aft
have split into two groups.
Jim, eyes up, they're
coming in from the rear!
[JIM]
Gotcha!
There they are!
Ain't gonna work, little lady!
[HORUS] Enemy craft have
anti-laser defenses.
Uh! Hilda, what're we gonna do?
[HILDA] Keep firing. It'll keep
them on their toes, at least.
Okay!
[laughs] Runnin' out of time!
[HORUS]
Further evasion is dangerous.
Now leaving guide path.
Grappler Ship closing
in from above!
Okay, lady!
Got ya this time!
Horus, we need a rapid climb!
[retches]
Aw, shit!
How much longer till we're
clear of the asteroid zone?
[HORUS]
482 seconds.
[groaning]
I see something that's
closing in on us ahead!
It's a large ship!
[HORUS]
Ship is cruiser-class.
Type, unknown. It is
on a collision course.
Send out a warning.
[HORUS] They claim they
have the right of way.
[AISHA]
This is the Orta Honehone ,
registered to the
Ctarl-Ctarl Empire.
I am speaking to you as
Ambassador Plenipotentiary
Aisha Clanclan,
with total authority
in all space held
by the Ctarl-Ctarl Empire!
We are docking at Blue
Heaven! Clear the way!
[CTARL CREW shouting]
[CTARL CREW]
Clear the way! Clear the way!
[CTARL A] Make way for
the Ctarl-Ctarl Empire!
[CTARL B] If you don't clear the
way, we're gonna whip your ass!
[OUTLAW C]
The Ctarl-Ctarl Empire?!
[OUTLAW B]
What should we do?
Like we really have a choice?
These guys are even
worse than pirates!
Listen, I'm an Outlaw.
I hate to say it,
but I don't have a treaty
with you, understand?
This departing ship is
taking the right of way.
Huh?! You're picking a fight
with the Ctarl-Ctarl?!
Hey, Jim, tell me, what're
the Ctarl-Ctarl like, again?
[JIM] They're like a cross
between a human and a tiger.
They're real nasty.
[CTARL C] Approaching ship
isn't changing course!
Wait! Wait a minute!
That's crazy!
[CTARL A]
Stop screwin' around!
[CTARL D]
Morons!
[CTARL E]
We're gonna eat you!
Don't you worry.
If you drop your shields,
there'll be enough
room for us to pass.
What?! Uh!
You defy the Ctarl-Ctarl
Empire?! [growls]
[CTARL A] If we don't do
something, we'll collide!
What?! Dodge them, idiots!
Dropping shields! Altering
course three degrees to port!
Firing starboard thrusters
for 10 seconds!
[whimpering]
[screaming]
Oh, boy.
Kay, go after 'em!
[AISHA]
Hey! Hold it right there!
All of you, stop your
ships, do you hear me?!
You're under arrest in the
name of Ctarl-Ctarl Empire!
[OUTLAW B]
Oh, no! What should we do?
[OUTLAW C]
What else can we do?!
We can't get away
from this ship!
[AISHA]
Hey! You, too, Outlaw!
Hold it!
[HORUS] T-minus-60 until
asteroid zone is cleared.
Warning...
Warning.
Further acceleration within
asteroid zone is dangerous.
[AISHA growling]
Damn it! 'Everyone's trying
to make fools of us!
That does it! Fire!
I said fire!
[CTARL CREW]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
[COUNSELOR]
But Lady Aisha,
firing within the
asteroid cluster is--
[AISHA growling]
Quiet!
This is in honor of
the Ctarl-Ctarl!
Y-Yes, ma'am.
[CTARL CREW]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
[growling]
[CTARL PILOT]
Lady Aisha blew it.
She should've listened to 'im.
So, Hilda, where are we
headed off to this time?
Just a little star system.
Meeting up with
some friends there.
[AISHA]
What?!
You mean, the Outlaw, Hilda!
That was her ship?!
Wow, Hilda's famous,
even in the empire.
She sure is.
Tell me where's she's headed!
Even if I knew I
wouldn't tell ya!
[BOTH growling]
These Outlaws will face
execution later!
Go after her at once!
But, we can't!
What are you saying?
Are you defying me?!
They are official
orders from home.
We are to remain here
until further instructed.
What? You mean to tell me you've
been in contact with home?
Of course, we were
ordered to contact them
once we had arrived
at Blue Heaven.
[AISHA screams]
Oh, God, are we there yet?
[HILDA]
No.
We have to go to sub-ether
three more times.
Argh!
[HORUS] Time required
to next sub-ether drive:
2 hours 10 minutes.
Get some rest, everyone.
Before I rest,
I have a question.
What the heck's
the Galactic Leyline?
That's simple,
it's a place that the Kei
Pirates are desperate to find.
[GENE]
Why?
Apparently, they say there's
some kind of huge treasure
that's suppose to
be hidden there.
One other thing.
Who's this MacDougall character?
Horus.
[HORUS]
The MacDougall Brothers.
They call themselves Outlaws,
but their position is unclear.
They will take any job from
anyone for the right price.
Other than that, no personal
information is available.
Why the hell are they pokin'
around your business?
Why don'tcha just ask 'em.
Hey, I gotta an idea,
this ship oughta have
some sleeping quarters.
Why don't you and I just
talk it over in bed.
Heh!
Would I get anything out of it?
Huh?!
[HILDA]
A cherry isn't worth my time.
I ain't a cherry!
[groaning]
Land this thing, I'll
show you whose a che--
Man, grown-ups and their
sleazy conversations...
Oh, you can't perform?
[BOTH]
Huh?!
Oh, sorry you can't perform.
That's too bad.
[BOTH]
Hm...?
[laughing]
The moon of that planet...
That's where we'll
meet my friends.
This is Horus.
Marx, O'Malley, come in, please.
[HILDA]
Anything on radar?
No. I'm not picking
up any spaceships.
Did you get here at the right
time, maybe we're just early?
They should've come
a long time ago.
[GENE]
You think you got stood up?
I doubt that.
I'm picking up something
on radar, but it's...
[HORUS] I'm picking it up
on the cameras, as well.
Enlarging.
I'm taking us in.
Oh, no.
That's the Leprechaun's
nose art!
[HORUS]
Debris ahead verified
as the Leprechaun
and the Purgatory.
I see a ship that's lifting
off from the moon's surface!
What?!
[MELFINA]
It's closing in at high speed.
[HORUS] Warning.
It's that pirate vessel.
[RON]
Just like I told you.
Hilda came, all right.
[RON] If you wanna
know about an Outlaw,
ask another Outlaw.
Heh!
[YOUNG GIRL]
Thank you, Mr. MacDougall.
Don't mention it.
I knew that the Guild would
pay for the information,
so it was an easy job.
Tell me, is there
any other way
I could be of any help to you?
My brother will launch our
ship, if you need us to.
This is our job now.
That won't be necessary.
You had to go and kill more
of my friends, didn't you?
So, what're we gonna do, now?
Accelerate and fly
down their throats.
Gene, take the gunner's chair.
You mean me?
I can fire that, but
I won't hit anything.
Just how long are you
gonna keep whining?!
If I can't hit anything,
I can't hit anything!
You gonna just keep
running away?!
Just keep running away?!
I'm not running.
Don't start bitching if
I puke on everything.
Wanna be a "Spacer," hold it in!
Aw, damn. What a slave-driver
Jim, I'll take over.
[JIM]
Hey, don't overdo it, Gene.
Ah, I'm a natural born Spacer,
don't you worry about it, Jim.
[OLD MAN chanting]
You won't get away, Hilda.
[HORUS] Pirate cub fighters
are approaching.
[HILDA] Lasers won't work
on them, use missiles!
Yeah, got it!
[screams]
[HORUS] Small craft has
made contact to starboard.
No damage.
Okay, wise-asses,
it's your turn to die!
[chuckles]
[RON]
You going to let them escape?
You needn't concern yourself.
[RON]
Oh?
[OLD MAN]
We've branded you, Hilda.
You will never be able
to escape us, now.
We will take back everything
that you stole from us.
You will regret
what you have done.
Head straight for
Farfallas, Horus.
Calculate sub-ether course.
[HORUS]
Roger.
Hey, where is this
Farfa-whatever place?
It's a star system about
40 light years from here
with a lot of natural resources.
It's a desert island in space.
So, why are we goin' there?
That ship I told you about
before is hidden there.
Huh? You actually gave me
a straight answer for once.
Because I found out I can
use you as a crew member.
Aw, what are you talkin' abou--
[groans]
Okie, dokie, Gene.
Off to the bathroom.
Hang in there.
[HILDA exhales]
[MELFINA
Um?
[HILDA]
Hm?
Why did you bring me along?
Would you have preferred to
stay back there with them?
Not really.
I would never mistreat you.
All right.
Once all spacecraft are aboard,
you can begin the pursuit.
[RON]
You need help tracking them?
I don't.
[RON]
In that case, I'll be going.
My brother is here
to pick me up.
This should prove
to be interesting.
[RON chuckles]
[CTARL GOVERNOR] This is a
disgrace, Aisha Clanclan.
Our reports clearly state
that Hilda's ship, Horus,
was right under your nose and
you dared to let him get away?
But, Governor at that time, uh,
I did not have that information!
Lady Aisha, that's simply a
Comm Cube you're looking at.
It's just a recording.
And therefore, Aisha Clanclan...
Your rank as ambassador
plenipotentiary
is hereby stripped.
You will remain at Blue Heaven
as a resident officer
and gather information regarding
the Galactic Leyline.
Oh, no, Governor, I beg of
you, that's way too harsh!
I'm telling you
he can't hear you.
The Orta Honehone will
depart Blue Heaven
and continue tracking Horus.
That will be all.
[CTARL CREW cheering]
[CTARL CREW]
Leave port! Leave port!
Oh, brother. Damn. Ah.
Isn't it a little hot in here?
[HILDA]
We're getting closer to the sun.
Hang in there.
Well, how much more closer
do you plan on taking us?
Just a little more.
Wha...? Oh, yeah, that's great.
Just a little closer, and
we'll dive right into it.
[HORUS]
I found it, Hilda.
[HILDA]
There it is.
That's a ship out there.
A very special ship,
one that's built with
the brains of the pirates
and the technology
of the Space Forces.
Space Forces and the pirates?
[HILDA] Matching orbit
with the asteroid.
I'm taking us in.
[HORUS]
Roger.
[GENE]
Okay, now I get it.
So the pirates were
after this baby, huh?
Now I'm convinced.
Hey, Hilda! Don't leave
me hangin' out here!
The space pirates flock towards
a mysterious spaceship that
was hidden on an asteroid!
We have to deal with some
bad luck that comes our way.
My long years of discipline
are being put to the test.
Next time, on Outlaw Star :
"When the Hot Ice Melts"!
You better get ready!