[NARRATOR]
A thief once opined:
"I may steal, but that
does not make me inhuman."
[NARRATOR]
Those Outlaws who are adrift
and roaming the universe say:
"You may not have the
urge to break the law,
but you are still
bound to ignore it."
[NARRATOR]
The blind and self-serving
vanity of the thief.
The archaic and old-fashioned
code of the pirate.
The vainglorious
and narcissistic
pride of the Outlaw.
These may merely be white lies
to delude themselves and others
that they may, to some extent,
be considered upright people.
Whether fact or fiction,
the Outlaws live by
and follow a code
that they take pride in.
On the other hand, ruffians
who live outside the law,
and follow no code at all, cause
some of the greatest calamities.
Gene, are you sure you wanna
go ahead with this thing?
Calm down.
All I gotta do is just
cut one of them, right?
[beeping]
If you cut the dummy wire,
it'll blow us to pieces!
So that means that we only
stand a fifty-fifty chance.
Hey, trust me!
You'd never guess it, but
gambling is my specialty!
Help me!
[CONTROL MAN A]
Dock 2-17, ready for entry.
[CONTROL MAN B]
Gorgeous Mitsuru ,
you're clear to come
in on route 7-A-12.
[CONTROL MAN C]
Number 382,
hurry up with
those preparations!
[GENE]
Ahh, this is killin' me!
I can't believe that
I'm stuck up here
sittin' around with this
loser spaceport tugboat job.
[GILLIAM]
I agree.
This is no job for the galaxy's
most advanced Grappler Ship.
[beeping]
Will you quit your whining!?!
You just got a request to do a
catch-and-release on an Ad Ship!
It's heading your
way on course 9C3,
you're to haul it back
to the spaceport now!
I mean, you humans are
always complaining every day
about not having work,
so now's your time...
Come on, Jim, will ya
close channel already?
You know what, if we help
out with the station job,
they'll give us discount
parking planet-side!
Now, you can't beat that.
[GILLIAM] Still, I don't
understand how they could use
the 1st place Privateer of
the space race as a tugboat?
Speaking of which,
it looks like the race
has been good advertising.
Well, it's making
us a laughing stock!
Damn it! Why is this
area so crowded,
where the hell is
everybody going?!
I heard there was a big time
jewelry store on the station
that was celebrating
some kind of renovation.
--[music plays]
--Huh?
Hey, that's it. That's the
Ad Ship Aisha mentioned!
[GENE groans]
Melfina, display the
rendezvous course!
[MELFINA]
Sure.
[AD SHIP] ...ring costs
only three months' salary...
[MELFINA]
It's huge!
Yeah, it's too big.
Sure it'll get your attention,
but it can't make sharp turns,
so getting it into port is
nothing but a giant hassle.
Like that's why they
need to use a tugboat?
Now, quit your yapping,
and let's get to work!
[MELFINA] Now matching
relative velocities.
Okay, locking... complete.
All right, I'll
begin deceleration
and put us on a docking course.
--[GENE] What's that?
--[JIM] Whoa!
What do they mean by "gotcha"?
[GILLIAM[
Virus penetration in progress.
Unable to purge.
System shutting down.
[gasps]
[MELFINA sighs]
The virus seeped into the system
right when those
anchors locked on.
Now, Gilliam has
completely shut down!
--Huh?!
--[COMM] Congratulations!
You are a lucky winner!
You've been selected to
go on a tour of heaven!
--What the hell?
--[beeping]
--Huh?
Aisha, we're busy right
now! Call back later!
[CRACKERJACK]
"Later" doesn't exist for people
who only have five
hours to live.
What? Who the hell are ya?
[CRACKERJACK]
Well now, let's see...
You can call me Crackerjack
for the time being.
For the time being?
[CRACKERJACK]
I suggest you remain calm.
My name is the least of your
problems at this moment.
The Ad Ship you're
presently connected to
happens to be loaded
with a high-yield bomb.
[JIM]
Uh... A bomb?
[CRACKERJACK]
If our demands are not met,
the bomb has been set with
an automatic detonator
which will blow itself up
along with your ship.
You have only...
...five hours.
That's ridiculous!
So what are these demands
of yours, anyway?
[CRACKERJACK]
Feast your eyes and listen.
I repeat, we, the
People's Liberation Front,
demand the immediate removal
of the Viceroy of Heifong
and any of his personal aides.
He is nothing but a puppet
of the Tempa Empire.
We expect total independence
granted to Heifong!
--Like the days on Old Earth!
--Independence?!
--Down with evil colonial rule!
--No way...
[CRACKERJACK]
You heard the man.
If our demands are
met unconditionally,
you will be set free.
Oh, right. I almost forgot.
The bomb is extremely delicate.
If you try and dismantle it,
it is programmed to
detonate immediately.
Please don't think of trying
anything... foolish.
Do enjoy yourselves, gentlemen.
--[MELFINA gasps]
--Oh, come on! Now what?
It's gonna blow!
Damn it, he's changed our orbit.
Mel! Calculate our orbit!
[MELFINA]
Right.
Okay, and Jim, you put
together a damage report.
[JIM]
I'm on it!
[NEWSCASTER]
The rage of the terrorist group,
the People's Liberation Front,
known to be highly aggressive,
has currently hijacked a
tugboat near the station,
and implores that Heifong be
granted its independence.
We can only imagine how
the Viceroy will respond
to such unheard-of demands.
[VICEROY] Heifong will
never be independent.
And we must never
give into terrorists,
not while we're out
here on the frontier.
[CIVIL SERVANTS]
Yes, sir!
Even if it means our sacrificing
the lives of the hostages.
[NEWSCASTER]
We now have confirmation on
the registration of
that captive tugboat!
Okay, so, who are the morons?
It has been determined that
the ship is the Outlaw Star .
The hostages are her captain,
Gene Starwind, plus two others.
Not Gene!
[JIM] I've purged the virus, but
the memory is pretty trashed,
so Gilliam is still offline.
The oxygen circulation
system's still working somehow,
but the temperature
regulator's shot.
Weapons and navigation are
pretty much gone, of course.
Attitude control is about
all we can do, at this point.
And the airlocks
won't open, either!
So then we couldn't abandon
ship as a last resort
even if we wanted to.
Well, is there anything
that does work?
From what I see, the only things
working are the Grappler Arms.
It looks like their system is
linked directly to the cockpit.
[growls]
[MELFINA]
I've calculated our orbit.
I'll put it on the screen.
We're circling above
Heifong III's equator
and losing altitude.
Damn! Then that means that even
if the bomb doesn't go off
in the five hours that they've
programmed it for, then--
We'll carry the bomb
right into the station
when we hit it, won't we?
[STATION PA]
An evacuation order
has been issued
for this station.
Will everyone please calmly
evacuate the station.
[screaming]
Wait! My jewels!
Getting out of here is
much more important, ma'am!
They're insured, you
don't have to worry.
[screaming]
[STATION PA]
Please remain calm!
There are more than enough
spaceship seats for everyone.
[CAPTAIN MITSURU] Gorgeous
Mitsuru , lifting off!
[CONTROL MAN A]
Head around to deck 28!
[CRACKERJACK]
Exactly according to plan.
[chuckles]
Commence operation!
[NEWSCASTER] Spaceships
are fleeing the station
one after another.
Calculations show that...
Gene! What's happening
up there? Tell me!
[GENE] Shut up, Aisha!
Jim, end transmission!
Will you stop telling
me to shut up?!
--[footsteps]
--[gasps]
[SUZUKA] Don't you know
that yelling at him
won't solve anything?
So what do you suggest we do?
It's very simple,
I'll go ask the man
who built the bomb
how to disarm it.
[gasps]
[SUZUKA] Asking the man behind
it is the most certain way.
[door opens, closes]
Huh?! Hey, wait!
But I don't understand
how you're gonna do that!
[CIVIL SERVANT A]
I've got bad news, Viceroy!
[VICEROY]
What is it?
[CIVIL SERVANT A]
The simulation of the bomb ship
hitting the station predicts
that the orbital elevator
will crash to the ground!
[CIVIL SERVANT B]
What?!
[CIVIL SERVANT C] Viceroy, we
mustn't endanger the planet!
We have no choice. We'll have
to blow it up with the hostages
before it comes
near the station.
[CIVIL SERVANT A]
But sir, that's what I, uh--
Viceroy, I must tell you that
according to the terrorists,
the ship is loaded
with large quantities
of radioactive material.
[growls]
Can't we do anything about it?!
[JIM] Gene, are you
really gonna do this?
Do you have any
other ideas, huh?
No, but it's crazy to
try and disarm a bomb
with an amateur like you!
Show some backbone!
Mel, I need you to
handle the scanning.
Right. Now beginning
infrared scan.
All we have to do is cut the
power connected to the fuse.
It's really no different
than cutting the cord
to an ordinary
spark plug, right?
Yeah, but, an engine
doesn't explode
when you happen to cut the
wrong cord to a spark plug.
The infrared scan
is now complete.
I'll put it up on the screen.
[GENE] What? There's nothing
there; it's mostly hollow.
'Cause it's camouflage.
That's how they got it
to pass inspection
before it started
the port entry course.
Hmph. So, we have no way
of telling what's inside,
unless we open the thing.
[SUZUKA] What about the owner
registration on the Ad Ship?
Surely, you have that.
But we can only give...
...that kind of information
out to the police!
Quit stalling and tell us
everything we want to know!
[screams]
We have gotta take
a look inside!
We just have to
take that chance.
[JIM]
Don't do it, Gene!
[MELFINA]
It's too dangerous.
Is that it?
Let's do it!
[chanting]
[gasps]
[GENE]
What the--?!
[BOTH gasp]
Gene!
[MELFINA]
I'm getting no response
from the tip of the
right Grappler Arm.
Other than that, there doesn't
seem to be any serious damage.
Damn, that scared
the hell outta me.
Exactly, so let's forget
the whole thing!
--[beeping]
--Huh?
Jim, quick, trace the signal!
I'm on it!
This is the Outlaw Star .
[CRACKERJACK] Didn't I tell you
not to try anything stupid?
Bite me! That was
just some stupid bluff!
I thought the whole thing was
supposed to blow us away!
[CRACKERJACK] No, no.
That isn't very smart, is it?
We'd lose everything if an
idiot like you set it off
before the Viceroy could
give into our demands.
If you try anything else again,
you won't get off
with just a warning.
I realize you're very
proud of this bomb, but...
I'm still gonna have
to try and disarm it.
You know, you should not
aggravate the terrorist!
[CRACKERJACK laughs]
That's a good one!
You blunder into the most
rudimentary of traps
and you think that you're
capable of dismantling
a bomb that I personally made?
Don't even try and out-smart me,
you little tugboat pilot!
Well, look who's talkin',
you're nothin' but
a useless mad bomber.
[CRACKERJACK chuckles]
If you insist, now I dare you.
Give it your best shot.
Good luck, Tugboat!
That jerk likes to
hear himself talk.
Did you get a trace on him?
It's hopeless.
Normal radio waves
don't have directivity.
But wait, there was no lag time,
so he's probably within at
least 30,000 kilometers or so.
Thirty-thousand, huh?
I'm not getting a signal
from any spaceships
within that radius.
Looks like they've
all evacuated.
Are they on the surface?
Are you nuts?!
You think they'd hang
around on the surface
when the orbital elevator
might come crashing down?
[GENE groans]
Where do you suppose
they've all gone, then?
Jim! Whaddya think, can we
send out a jamming signal?
A jamming signal?
Uh-- Well, the comm
system is working,
so I guess Î can come
up with something.
[keyboard clicking]
[beeping]
Huh?
[CRACKERJACK]
Oh...
[chuckles]
Looks like Tugboat
has a brain, after all.
[thumping]
There's a pitch
change over here.
This is the only section
where the sound is different.
Great, that's it, Mel!
Jim, can I use the torch gun?
No, it's hooked up
to the power system.
The buzz saw has internal
batteries, though.
You can use that.
[chanting]
[GENE]
Bingo! That's it!
[JIM] Forget it!
This is the real thing!
Here goes...
[gasps]
[beeping]
Wise guy... why'd you
have to do that?
[MELFINA]
That small, tube-like object
appears to be a detonator.
I can't determine
whether the explosives
are directly inside or not.
You see those two
wires over there?
One of them carries the
signal to the detonator.
Then, what do you suppose
the other one's for?
Hey, don't worry about it;
I grew up watching tons of
movies with bombs in 'em.
The instant the
dummy wire is cut,
it sets off a relay that
sends a signal to the real one.
And then... boom!
So what are you thinkin' of?
Whelp, there's only one
thing for me to do, Jim.
Gene, are you sure you wanna
go ahead with this thing?
Calm down.
All I gotta do is just
cut one of them, right?
If you cut the dummy wire,
it'll blow us to pieces!
So that means that we only
stand a fifty-fifty chance.
Hey, trust me!
You'd never guess it, but
gambling is my specialty!
Help me!
[GENE]
The red...
...or the blue?
With this much explosives,
if I screw up, we're all
gonna be dead anyway.
--[JIM laughs]
--Huh?
[laughing continues]
I can't believe at a time
like this, you're laughing.
Come on, Jim, you're
bigger than that.
Yeah, but when
I'm really scared,
these things seem funny, and
I can't seem to explain it...
I just know that I
can't stop laughing.
[GENE groans]
[JIM laughs]
I know it's crazy...
Huh?
It'll be okay.
I know everything will work out.
Thanks, Mel...
So, whaddya say we
test our luck now?
[GENE]
Let's do it!
--[beeping]
--[yelps]
What is it?!
Didn't you send out
a jamming signal?
It's a directional
laser transmission!
And it's coming
from the station.
The station?!
Whaddya mean?
Someone's still there?
What do you think you're doing?!
Aisha?!
It's been hard to reach you; we
couldn't get you on the radio!
What in the hell are you
doing on the station?!
[AISHA] I tracked the
scent of the terrorist,
and it seems to
have led me here!
[GENE]
His scent?
[SUZUKA]
That's not true.
We tried to track down
information on the ship's owner,
but it was a dummy, so we
found ourselves in a corner.
[AISHA] So we asked Fred Luo,
and he gave us the information!
[GENE]
Fred, huh?
Huh. I bet that really cost you.
Not at all.
Actually, he was most
cooperative when I told him
it was to help you.
[AISHA] He even lent us a
shuttle for free to get up here!
So, what information
did you get?
Well, you see, according to Luo,
the Ad Ship's registration
is actually a fake that was sold
by pirates on the black market!
[GENE]
Pirates?!
So then, after that,
we had Luo check and see
who the pirates had
previously sold it to.
Will ya just get to the point?
Who the hell did he sell it to?
The buyer was the lead-man of
a notorious gang of robbers.
[VICEROY]
I can't sacrifice the lives
of everyone on Heifong III.
The Viceregal of Heifong
agrees to your demands.
We recognize Heifong's
independence!
Perhaps you misunderstood me.
What we're looking
for here and demand
is recognition by
the Tempa Empire.
Any decision made
by the Viceregal
is totally useless to us.
[VICEROY] What?!
Don't tell me at this point
that you never had
any intention of--
What, this guy's not
even a terrorist?
He's just a simple thief?
I'm not sure I understand.
Why would robbers demand
Heifong's independence?
I can't believe it!
This whole bomb scare is a sham!
Ugh! It was all just a decoy,
so they could empty
out the space station!
But why, Gene? I don't get it.
[chuckles]
[cackles]
I know exactly how you
think now, Mr. Crackerjack.
I bet this is a dummy, too.
It'll explode no matter
which cord I cut!
Uh, If that's not it,
where's the real detonator?
I'm gonna take a look inside
that hatch that blew up first.
If my hunch is right, the
detonator's inside there!
Oh, I get it.
You would never
check a place again
that you've already looked at.
Bulkhead!
I hear a faint mechanical sound.
That's it, all right.
Jim. Can I still
use the buzz saw?
Well, if you're just
gonna cut a small hole,
the batteries oughta hold!
Okay, this time we're
gonna get this sucker!
But even if you find the
real detonator in there,
what will you if you
find two cords again?
This guy's really
full of himself.
He'd most likely think
it was beneath him
to use the same trap.
But if he did, I rely on my
intuition and my good luck!
All right, it's time.
[CRACKERJACK]
Let's do it!
Huh?!
Who are you?
[SUZUKA] I believe that's
our line... Crackerjack.
Robbery under the
disguise of terrorism.
Well, you must think
you're very, very clever.
[sighs] How'd you figure it out?
I really can't stand
bastards like you
who think they can plan
out every little thing!
Kill 'em! Now!
[ROBBERS yells]
[AISHA hisses]
[roars]
[CRACKERJACK grunting]
[SUZUKA] And looks like
you're the only one left...
--...Crackerjack.
--[CRACKERJACK gasps]
Uh, uh... Just tell me
what is it you two want.
I'll cut ya a deal.
[laughs nervously] If you
two want part of the take,
how does half of it sound?
You realize that the
ship with the bomb
is headed straight
for the station.
We're almost out of time here!
Oh, yes, that.
Don't worry about it.
--What? Huh? Huh?
--[ship whirring]
[CRACKERJACK groaning]
[gasps]
Well! We finally get
to meet, Crackerjack!
You?! That's impossible!
Oh, yeah, it's possible.
After we disarmed your bomb,
we ditched it and came straight
here to pay you a visit.
You son of a-- Ah!
[CRACKERJACK groaning]
That was a fun five
hours, Crackerjack.
[CRACKERJACK growls] Bastard!
[grunts]
[yells]
[groans]
[CRACKERJACK groans]
The countdown... is over.
[GENE] Those Kei guys have
finally gotten serious,
and now they're
trying to wipe us out.
There's seven of 'em!
Who do I look like, Snow White?
This isn't gonna be easy.
They have all kinds of
tricks up their sleeves.
Anyway, looks like this story
is finally getting interesting!
But the taking care of it
is what makes it difficult.
Will somebody please get me
some more money for this gig?!
Next time, on Outlaw Star :
"The Seven Emerge"!
You better get ready!