[NARRATOR] On the so
called "Frontier of Space,"
areas more than 50 light
years away from Earth.
The degree of punishment
has become severe
in proportion to the flagrant
disregard for the law there.
A criminal arrested after
just one serious crime,
will immediately receive the
death penalty after a swift,
simple trial.
The infamous prison built
on the high-gravity world
of Hecatoncheir, Is also a
product of this harsh system
of frontier justice.
Since the day it opened,
it has come to be known as a
hellish place where time moves
at a snail's pace and no has
ever managed to come out alive.
Naturally, there is no instance
of a successful escape attempt.
So far, that is.
[TRANSPORT PILOT]
Hecatoncheir Orbital Station,
this is prisoner transport 109.
I have one prisoner
currently on board.
Request docking clearance.
[DECK OFFICER]
Roger, you are cleared.
[PRISON AI]
Prisoner Curse Hawkwind.
Sentenced to life imprisonment
for Class One murder, robbery,
rape and 17 other
felonious crimes.
[WARDEN] This one should
prove to be amusing.
Send him down at once.
[WARDEN] Is this your
only personal effect?
[GENE] Yeah, that's my
good luck charm.
Take good care of it, will ya?
[WARDEN]
What's taking you so long?
Take your food tray
and sit down now!
I hear you ran like a
wild man on the outside,
but if you can't learn to
move in gravity this low,
you'll never survive
very long in here, Curse.
You're so pathetic!
Three G's is nothing!
Up in the punishment
facility at the North Pole,
Ten G's is what you can expect.
At this rate you'll probably
die of massive heart failure
or a brain aneurism before
your sentence is up!
[chuckles]
[WARDEN] Hey, what are
you wobbling around for?
Start walking, damn you!
[grunts]
[WARDEN] Stand up,
and pull yourself together,
you good-for-nothing!
Easy, come on now, Jake.
You don't wanna be making
any trouble for the warden.
[WARDEN] Saiyo! This is
none of your business.
[SAIYO grunts]
[WARDEN] Don't try to dodge me.
Hold still, damn it!
[SAIYO chuckles] Sorry about
that man, I-I guess I slipped.
[WARDEN] Silence! I've had
enough of your yapping!
[GENE grunts]
[WARDEN] And what do
you think you're doing?
Why don't you put down
the puppet for a minute
and come out to meet me
face to face like a man?
How about it buddy?
[WARDEN] You bastard!
You'll pay for this!
[GENE mockingly laughs]
[GENE grunts]
Hey! Wait a munite!
[grunts]
You two think you're smart, huh?
Well, you just earned 24 hours
in the punishment facility.
Curse, you just
arrived here at Gehenna,
so it's time that you
learned what real fear means.
Let this serve as
a final warning
to all you other prisoners.
You are under
constant surveillance.
There's no use trying to
escape from this prison
and there's no
defying me either!
[WARDEN laughs]
You've got a serious
death wish, buddy.
Deliberately trying to
start something like that.
And what do you call
what you were doing?
[WARDEN] I don't want
to hear another word
out of either one of you!
Now get on board!
[BOTH grunt]
[grunts] That guy really likes
to play rough, doesn't he?
[SAIYO]
Ah, he's always like that.
[GENE grunts]
Maybe I shouldn't of
push the limit so much.
[GENE]
You mean Planet Hecatoncheir?
[KHAN]
Yes, that's right!
It's a strange world
that's very massive
for an Earth-type planet.
It has an incredibly
high rotational speed,
and a gravity of 1G
along its equator.
It's shaped like an intricate
string of beads on an abacus.
Hey, Gilliam!
[GILLIAM] Yes. Just a moment,
I'll pull up the data.
What's an abacus, anyway?
The point is, it's not the
shape that's the problem,
it's the gravity.
The force pushing down
on the planet varies
depending upon where you are.
It's a crushing
10.4G's at the poles,
even though it's still 3G's
where the prison is situated.
[JIM] Then I guess
you'd weigh three times
what you normally would.
That's right, Jim.
What a smart boy to figure
that out so quick.
At any rate, there isn't a
single area in the prison
where the gravity is stabilized.
As a matter of fact,
for security reasons,
you can't find a
gravity stabilized area
anywhere on the entire planet.
Due to its high
rotational speed,
the whole planet acts as a
huge dynamo, generating a
powerful magnetic
field around the globe.
The result is that radios
and radar don't transmit
or receive as well
on the surface.
And in human time,
one day is 74 minutes.
Just thinking about
it makes me sick.
I didn't realize
that Gehenna Prison
is on planet Hecatoncheir.
No wonder why no one has
ever gotten out alive.
Gene, you've got to be careful.
Your usual recklessness
won't serve you well
if you want to take
on this mission.
She's right. Use your
head this time.
If you jump in without
thinking, it's all over!
Yeah, like you're one to talk!
Gene, come on...
You say that no one's
ever gotten out alive, huh?
All right then what
are we waiting for?
[GENE]
Where are Suzuka and Aisha?
[JIM] Just like you said,
Aisha's with Mel,
and Suzuka's sticking
to Gwen Khan like glue.
All right, Jim, now don't
let your guard down.
[JIM]
Mm-hm.
Khan, did you get a
chance to look into what
I was asking you for?
Yes, as a matter of fact I've
got it right here with me.
A monopole.
I don't know what you're
going to use it for,
but bear in mind that
it's even more expensive
and more rare than Dragonite,
so make sure you return it to me
when you're finished using it.
Yeah, sure, I got it.
I understand what you're saying.
So anyway, were you able
to rig it like we discussed?
Of course. I camouflaged
it well, if I do say so myself.
It's an incredible piece of work
that would cost a small fortune
if it was made by someone else.
If you do say so yourself.
[GENE]
See you later, Jim.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, Sir!
[BOTH grunting]
[GENE grunts]
No small talk. Just get
right to the rough stuff.
[grunting]
This goddamn bed's in
here just to torture us.
I can't get up. Gimme a hand.
[SAIYO] Hey. Take it easy,
newbie. Don't move around.
[GENE]
Hmph.
[SAIYO] Don't worry,
the warden isn't listening.
His radio only operates inside
the main prison compound.
They don't have the budget to
lay wires all the way up here
just to allow him
to run the robots
and cameras to
keep an eye on us.
[GENE] So why did they build
this thing in the first place
if he can't even see us?
As a lesson to all
the other prisoners.
It's overkill, though.
There's no chance you can run
away in this 10G hell hole.
[GENE] Yeah, I feel like
I'm gonna pass out
if I don't get out of here soon.
--[GENE grunts]
--[SAIYO laughs]
[SAIYO] I'm surprised you
managed to talk this much
on your first trip
to the cooler.
I'm Saiyo Wong.
Who are you?
[chuckles] Well isn't
that a coincidence?
That makes things easier.
Saiyo Wong, How perfect.
You're the man... that I
came in here to see.
What did you say?
[GENE] I wanted to ask
you the coordinates...
...of the Galactic Leyline.
[SAIYO]
The Galactic Leyline?
Why don't you tell me who
you are first, boy?
[GENE] Just an ordinary
Outlaw passin' by.
What are you an idiot?
Even if I did tell
you the coordinates,
there's no way
to get out of here.
Relax, kid. Now that you're in,
you'll never get out.
[GENE]
You gotta be kiddin'.
You think I'm gonna spend
the rest of my life in here,
rottin' in a prison cell?
If you want to, you can
tag along with me.
Are you in, or you out?
Moron.
[GENE]
What's that?
Hey, man, what's it
gonna be? Huh, Saiyo?
Come on, Saiyo! What do you say?
[GENE] It's pretty nice
of them to bring us back
after only one day,
don't ya' think?
I can't believe that
3G could feel so light.
I'm cruisin'!
If you do something
dumb like jumping,
your bones will snap in
two like toothpicks, pal.
Oh. Well look who's talking.
I knew if I was annoying enough
you'd finally say something.
So, Wong, are you interested in
what I've been talking about?
Huh?
Wait a minute, Wong!
--[alarms blaring]
--[GENE] Huh?
What the hell?
Gentlemen, it's been a
long while but a courageous,
if not foolish, man has
revealed himself
among our distinguished
inmate guest list.
That man is none other
than Nikolai Illivich,
who was invited to this prison
17 days ago, Sol Standard Time.
He destroyed an entire prison
wall using explosives that
he had cleverly hidden
inside his body before
attempting his failed
escape from the facility.
You certainly don't see a heroic
attempt like this very often.
[PRISONERS cheering]
Why don't we take a look and see
how he's making out, shall we?
[gasps]
--[grunts]
--[mechanical humming]
[NIKOLAI screams]
[SAIYO]
Now do you get it?
At 3G there's nowhere to hide
in that barren wasteland,
even if you did manage
to get beyond those walls.
They're on top of you
before you know it,
and even if you
manage to lose 'em,
the only place you can
run is the to the equator,
where the gravity is weak.
They'll circle ahead
of you, and it's all over.
There's no way to escape from
this prison, end of story!
Yeah, well, how do
you know it won't work
if you've never even tried it?
What a moron!
[coughs]
[WARDEN]
All right, next in line.
Hey, what's up, Wong.
[WARDEN]
There's absolutely no talking!
Come on, what's the big deal.
I just wanted to say hi!
[GENE grunts]
I was wondering what kind
of monster I'd find here
when I heard that you're a
bigshot in the Battle Group.
An outfit that gives the Kei
Pirates a run for their money.
But you're just another
pathetic little man who's
waiting to die of
heart failure, I guess.
And here I thought
you had some potential,
but you're just another dumb
crook who only knows how
to shoot off his mouth and
make an ass of himself.
Hey, I'm not a criminal,
I'm an Outlaw!
If you wanna call
yourself an Outlaw, fine.
But don't let that reckless
death wish of yours
get anybody else killed!
Oh, yeah? Reckless?
Well, no Outlaw would sit
around and wait to die
in this god-forsaken hellhole
when he's got
nothing left to lose.
If there's just
the slimmest chance,
no matter how small,
you have to go for it.
Never give up hope.
And that's what it
means to be an Outlaw!
You think I'm putting up
with this because I want to?
Well, you're right.
There's nothing left to
lose in this hellhole!
Do you know that no one has
ever served out his sentence
and left this prison alive?
Everyone's heart
eventually gives out,
and they die before
their sentence is up.
This gravity is too much
for humans to survive.
The place is just a total
bloodless execution ground!
[grunts]
Huh?
You guys want somethin'?
If I'm not mistaken,
you're the little bastard who's
been bugging Mr. Wong lately.
[GENE]
You Saiyo's bitches?
[chuckles]
You better watch your
dirty mouth, pretty boy.
What you don't understand,
is that Mr. Wong looks after us,
even if it involves going
up against the damn warden.
A punk like you don't have
any business hanging around.
[chuckles]
If he's content to
be the leader
of a pack of whipped dogs,
then Saiyo Wong ought to
just quit while he's ahead.
You asshole!
[JOSE grunts]
Got 'em.
[ALL grunting]
[PRISONER 1]
What's all the ruckus about?
[PRISONER 2] They say there's
a fight in the sauna room.
When they know they'll
get sent to the cooler?
Who's the moron?
[PRISONER 2]
Looks like Jose and the others
are puttin' the new
guy in his place.
[GENE]
Who's side are you on anyway?
Damn it, I'm taking
crap from everybody!
Aren't you fighting
the wrong guy?
Ever thought about giving
that warden a hard time
--instead of me?
--[SAIYO chuckles]
[scoffs]
[SAIYO]
You stand out too much.
Don't you get it?
You've got too much spirit.
What's that supposed to mean?
[SAIYO] Everybody wants
to escape from here so bad
they can't stand it. But they
can't do anything about it.
They can either do something
crazy and die like Illivitch,
or they can give up on
everything and wait to die.
To people lie that,
you stand out like an eyesore
because you've got
too much spirit.
[GENE]
Does that go for you, too?
What was that, pal?
What about you, Wong,
are you throwing in the towel
and giving up
on everything, too?
That's what I mean.
That's the attitude
that's pissing people off!
As if I'd ever just
give up all hope
and wait to die in a
concrete bunker like this!
Okay then, what would you
do if I told you that I had
a surefire escape plan to
get us out of this place?
Huh?
Ringside seats!
We got a fight on!
[grunts]
[grunting]
Mr. Wong's finally
gonna teach a lesson
to that smart ass new guy!
[PRISONER 3] Don't let those
damn robots interfere!
Anybody out there want to
bet a meal on the new guy?
[PRISONER 4]
Where is it? Where's the fight?
Over there? I can't see it!
[grunts]
Bastard!
[WARDEN] Stop it immediately,
both of you!
[BOTH grunting]
Get ready to die, you punk!
[grunts]
You first, asshole!
--[BOTH growl]
--[WARDEN] Hold it!
What do you think
you two you're doing?
If you've got that much energy,
I'll make sure you burn it off
Forty eight hours in the
punishment facility!
Starting right now!
Whatever you say.
Take it easy!
Getting mad is bad
for your blood pressure.
[WARDEN]
Not another word!
[GENE]
I'm asking you once again.
Can't you yell at
anybody face to face
instead through a camera lens?
[growls]
You little...!
[GENE grunts]
Ow damn, that hurts!
You just had to open
your mouth, didn't ya'?
Geez, I still can't believe
I trusted an idiot like you.
I guess I must be losing
my edge or something.
So anyway, did you get what
you were looking for in there?
Yeah, how about you?
You mean this?
[PRISON AI]
Warning! Warning!
Abnormality on Linear Car 002.
Car is out of control
and running wild.
[WARDEN]
What the hell?
[BOTH grunting]
Are you absolutely sure that
doin' this is such a great idea?
Everything's gonna be alright.
Even if we try and jump the
train tracks at the next stop,
the gravity's so strong that we
oughta stop right away at least.
I think so.
I hope it works.
[SAIYO]
Hey, wait a minute!
[WARDEN]
Get to work and do something!
[PRISON AI] I am sorry, but it
is totally out of my control.
To stop the train,
it is necessary to shut down the
entire transportation system.
Do I have permission
to initiate a shutdown?
I can't do that! Are you crazy?
[PRISON AI]
Linear Car 002
has crashed through the
punishment center gate.
Now plowing through snowfield.
They think they can
outsmart me, do they?
Capture them at once
and bring them here!
I'll make them wish that
they'd never been born!
[mechanical humming]
Everything's gone smoothly
according to your plan so far,
but what do we do now, huh?
That's where this baby comes in.
Oh, the good luck charm.
What do you plan on
doing with that thing?
You gonna start
praying or somethin'?
[GENE] You see, it's not
an ordinary compass.
There are two monopoles,
magnetic particles
with just one pole
except it's designed to
resemble a regular compass.
You got some kinda
trick up your sleeve?
Yeah somethin' like that. Huh?
[WARDEN]
Curse! Wong!
Give up, there's no escape.
If you surrender peacefully,
I'll make sure that you
granted a quick death.
[WARDEN chuckles]
Yeah, why don't you
bite me, you slowpoke!
This is really too bad, Wong.
Just when we were having
such a wonderful time here.
What, hey?!
Okay now, listen up.
If I'm not mistaken this
is the north pole, right?
Now the south attracts,
and the north repels.
But a magnetic monopole
plays by its own rules
because it only has one pole.
So the south monopole will
be pulled into the ground
while the--Oops!
And conversely, the north
monopole will be sent
flying upward along
the magnetic field line.
[SAIYO]
Huh?
[yells]
Even if somebody came up
with such a crazy idea,
who in their right mind would
ever believe that it would work?
How high are you
planning to go up, anyway?
That depends on when
our ride shows up.
But in the meantime, I'd suggest
that you start praying that my
buddies have the good sense
to fly as low as possible.
You're nuts, Curse!
I'm never gonna work
with you again! I mean it!
[GENE laughs]
I might as well tell you now,
my real name's not Curse.
It's Gene. Gene Starwind.
[SUZUKA] I'm picking up
a magnetic signature.
It's currently rising
over the north pole.
You guys it's Gene!
Okay, it's pretty much
empty over the pole.
We're gonna go in there and do
a catch and go at full speed!
[GILLIAM]
Understood.
[PRISON AI] Sub-ether signature
detected above the planet
and is descending
near the north pole.
[WARDEN]
What did you say?
Huh? Impossible!
That can't be happening!
[WARDEN]
This can't be!
After them!
If they get away, I'll be
ruined. You understand?
After them!
Hunt them down, dammit!
[PRISON AI]
No one can get to them in time.
Not even from the port
in stationary orbit.
Ah, Damn them!
Man, I bet that warden's
having a fit right about now.
I sure would love
to see his face.
Get serious.
Even if he's crying, I never
want to see his face again.
[laughs]
That's for sure.
[JIM]
Hey, Gene! Great job!
Thanks.
[KAHN] Well there! Well done,
well done, young man.
You should be quite proud
of the work you've done.
What about the Leyline?
Have you asked about
the Leyline coordinates?
Haven't you asked yet?
Mel comes first.
Yes, that's right. I'm sorry.
Oh, what a bother,
what a bother!
"Breakfast is signaled
with a silver spoon."
Hey, it worked!
You okay, Melfina?
How're you doing, Melfina!
Huh? Wha?
Gene, you look
different somehow.
When did you
change your clothes?
[GENE, JIM]
Uh...?
Well, you're satisfied, right?
Now hurry up and ask
about the Leyline.
[grunts]
Sorry, but someone had
to put you in your place.
That's right. The guy's a moron.
You can use this guy's
spaceship, if you hurry up.
He's out cold now.
In return, do me a favor
and ditch him someplace
along the way?
Would that be after I kill him?
[GENE]
No, look.
I told you before.
I'm an Outlaw, not a criminal.
I'll leave him alone.
Analyze this when
you get a chance.
There's a data file in it.
The password's "Miranda".
It also happens to
be my daughter's name.
That's a nice name.
Course it is, I'm the
one who gave it to her.
Anyway, the data file contains
The Leyline's coordinates.
After that you can go get
yourself killed for all I care.
Never want to see
an Outlaw again.
[chuckles]
[BOTH laugh]
[GENE] With the Galactic
Leyline waiting right under
our noses, We visit a planet
in search of Caster shells
to complete our armory.
While there, we come
across a couple of wise men
and a very mysterious woman.
Wait...
I see before me a paradise of
sexy ladies panting with desire!
Oh. it's so good to be alive!
Thank you, God!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Be sure to be there.
Next time on Outlaw Star:
"Hot Springs Planet Tenrei"!
You better get ready!
Fever! Fever! Fever!