[NARRATOR] The difference
between humans and robots
is obvious to anyone.
There are clear differences
between living and
non-living entities.
But what about the differences
between humans and cyborgs?
This is not a problem either.
A cyborg is someone who
has superhuman abilities
due to mechanical systems
that have been incorporated
into his body.
But how do we begin to
classify these bio-androids?
Actually, this gives rise
to ethical problems
that become
progressively complicated.
If one were to classify
a bio-android,
it would be have to be
thought of as a life form.
Because a cyborg is considered
a person, a bio-android,
in which machinery is
combined with flesh,
must also be
classified as a person.
However, most humans
scoff at such ideas
and insist that these
hybrids life forms
can never be regarded as humans.
This is because humans
were created by God,
but androids were created
solely by humans.
Their justification is that we
humans have souls that live on,
but androids live only
in the physical plane,
without any possibility
of life in the hereafter.
However, the existence
of a creator God,
and even the soul for that
matter, has yet to be discovered
and proven beyond
a shadow of a doubt
by any established organization
within the scientific community.
And so, the classification
of bio-android life forms
remains unclear.
[PRIEST] Did you like any one
of our paintings in particular?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I guess I kind of took you
by surprise a little there.
No. Really, it's my fault
entirely. I'm so sorry.
I shouldn't have come
in without asking.
[PRIEST] Oh, I don't mind
at all, my little one.
I consider it a distinct honor
to have another race
visit our Silgrian shrine,
I assure you.
Make yourself right at home.
Oh, now remember, there's
nothing for you to worry about.
It's not our place to try
and convert others.
Oh...
Is something troubling
you, young lady?
It's just... I don't
understand who I am
or why I was born in this world.
Well! That's a rather
complicated question, isn't it?
If you want to talk to someone
about the meaning of existence,
you've come to the right place.
Oh! That's okay!
Thanks for the offer,
but I've actually found
someone already
who promised that he'd
find the answer for me.
It's just that lately,
I wonder if he's
forgotten his promise
or if he's forgotten about me.
If that's what troubling you,
then I'll answer it with a quote
from Silgrian dogma
that fits the occasion.
It simply says that, "When
two people have lost faith
in each other,
then all is lost."
Do you understand?
Yes.
[door opens]
What took so long, Ron?
I guess I kept you
waiting a long time.
I got fed up with all
this waiting around,
and I was deciding
whether I should
just leave without you or not.
Hm. I finally finished
lining up the job.
We can take it now
that we've got you
and your new arm conditioned.
You mean...?
[RON]
Yeah.
We're gonna pay them a visit
and teach them once and for all
what happens to people who mess
with the MacDougall Brothers.
Hey, I'm back!
[JIM]
Hey there, Mel!
[GENE]
Hey, how much longer?
Will you hold your
horses, Gene?
I found this stupid
piece of crap
at the city garbage dump, okay?
Hey, what're you guys doing?
We just got delivered some
video mail from Clyde today.
Who's Clyde?
You know, he's the owner
of our favorite bar,
that neighborhood dive we took
you to back on Sentinel III.
We sent him our address here
and we just got a response.
It's all ready, Gene!
I'm gonna play it.
Are you sure that this
thing's recording?
Yeah, it's recording.
Gene! Jim! How are
you guys doing?
What a surprise!
We've been so worried since that
ruckus at Virginia Spaceport.
But I never actually
gave up hope.
Anyway, we're both
glad you're okay.
[IRIS] So I hear you've set
up shop in Heifong, huh?
Knowing you two, I bet you're
making money hand over fist!
[CLYDE] If you're in Heifong,
you're in a really big city.
There's no comparison between
the scale of business here
and a place like that.
When you two guys make it big,
stop by and say hello.
We'll be waiting.
Well, you take care now.
We'll send you another
message soon.
Hey, this is just like
old times, isn't it?
Yeah, but it's only been
a little over three months
since we left.
[GENE] Man, what I wouldn't give
for one of Clyde's spicy omelets
right about now, you know?
I was just thinkin' about Iris's
homemade custard pudding.
[GENE]
Yeah.
Oh well.
[beeping]
Hi!
You've reached the famous
Starwind and Hawking Repair Shop
where we guarantee
to fix anything
that can break down
in your life,
from tractors to relationships.
Is it true that
you'll also take jobs
that are considered by most
to be a little dangerous?
Heh. Well sure, as long as
it's not against the law.
It's not exactly illegal,
but it's possibly fatal.
Huh?
Well then, it'll depend
on the pay.
Like for starters, sir, could
you give us your full name?
My name is irrelevant.
I wanna meet so I can
talk to you in person.
In that case, feel free to come
on down to our office anytime.
No. I've chosen a
neutral location.
There's a restaurant called
Hellenism at Darien Point;
we'll meet there.
I think that you're just a
little confused, my friend!
Come on, you think we'd
be so incredibly stupid
that we'd go down
there on your terms
without discussing either
the job or the pay?
You'll come.
Believe me, it won't seem like
a waste of time at all.
I'd like to take a moment
to discuss with you
the Galactic Leyline.
Huh?
[JIM]
[MELFINA]
Huh?
Where did you find
out about that?
How could you possibly
get this number?
Who are you?
I have a table for two
reserved for five o'clock.
Only one of you will
come into the restaurant.
I'd advise you be
completely unarmed.
I'll be waiting.
Hey, hold on there!
[GENE]
Ugh!
Were you able to trace it?
Mm, let's see.
It was from a public phone
somewhere on J Street.
But I can't tell
who made the call.
Sorry.
Well, that's no surprise.
Restaurant Hellenism.
By car, it'll take you somewhere
around 40 minutes to get there.
Whoa!
Gene, it says here that typical
dinners start at 820 wong!
[GENE] This has trap
written all over it.
Think it's the pirates?
Well sure, it's possible,
but that's not exactly
what my gut's tellin' me.
Who then?
It doesn't really matter.
He mentioned the
Galactic Leyline,
so that means I have to go.
Get the car ready.
'Kay, you got it!
Gene, can I go?
[GENE]
Keep an eye on things here.
But, Gene.
I want to know too about
the Galactic Leyline!
If the job's on the up and up,
we'll tell you all about it
when we get back.
But if it turns into a blood
bath, you'd be better off here.
I know, but...
Don't worry, Melfina.
We'll come back in one piece,
I promise ya that.
[JIM]
Man! This place looks expensive!
Okay, Gene.
If you need me, I'll be on
standing by in the parking lot.
[GENE]
Right.
[MAITRE 'D] Your table, sir.
Enjoy your meal.
I knew that you'd
change your mind.
Please, have a seat.
[MAITRE 'D]
Take your time, gentlemen.
Well?
I wanna propose
a deal to you.
A deal?
I thought I came here
to discuss a job
that had to do with
the Galactic Leyline.
I wanna know if you would
agree to sell me your ship
and the girl that acts
as its control computer.
Sorry, pal. Neither
one of them's for sale.
Huh? Wait a minute.
How do you know about Melfina?
I heard about it from
my little brother.
Your little brother? Huh?
Are you telling me that you're
the older MacDougall brother?
That's right.
I knew you'd catch on quick.
You bastard!
The Galactic Leyline.
Now that I've got
your attention,
do you have any idea what it is?
don't know, but I would
imagine your killing Hilda
had something to do with it.
It was nothing personal.
I was just carrying
out a contract.
I just happened to be doing some
checking around afterwards,
and discovered a few stray facts
I think you might find
especially interesting.
[GENE] Really? What do
you mean by "facts"?
Start talking!
To make the journey to a place
called the Galactic Leyline,
the Kei Pirates needed
a specially equipped ship
and navigation system.
The only ship that can make
such a trip is yours: The XGP.
And the only navigation
system precise enough
is the bio-android girl.
[GENE] I know for a fact
Hilda kept that ship a secret!
[RON] That ship wasn't
designed and constructed
by the pirates alone.
It was completed in secrecy
with considerable assistance
from a Space Forces group.
Incidentally, the ship
and the android
were both stolen by Hilda.
So you helped out the pirates
and killed Hilda, is that it?
No, not at all. The only way
I helped out the pirates
was by finding Hilda.
The actual request
to destroy the XGP
came from the Space Forces,
who were afraid
that their dealings with
the pirates would come out.
At the time, they didn't explain
what kind of ship the XGP was
or its capabilities.
But that doesn't change the
fact that you're the one
who killed Hilda.
I'll get to that point.
But before I do,
I want the XGP and the
bio-android girl, Melfina.
I'll never give them to a
blood-sucking parasite like you.
Have it your way.
But just remember
that if you keep them,
they won't be used for
their original purpose.
Then there's just one other
thing that I need to ask you.
Yeah, what is it?
Are you the guys who
destroyed a cargo ship
near Sentinel III six years ago?
I gotta know.
Six years ago? Near Sentinel?
I don't remember
anything like that.
Yes, you do, you lying bastard!
I saw your ship with
my own two eyes!
In that case, I suppose it's
possible I've forgotten.
I've been rather busy
lately in my line of work.
I can't recall every
little job I've done.
[GENE]
You call that a little job?
Let me help you remember.
How 'bout starting
from the beginning
and telling me everything
that you know.
I thought I told you this
afternoon to come unarmed.
I didn't have any guarantee
you would be unarmed, did I?
No, I guess you didn't.
I think you've
insulted my friends.
I hate to disappoint you,
but you're not the only one who
brought along some friends.
Come back here!
[RON] These are the latest
Space Forces weapons.
I'm told they're
extremely powerful.
You're gonna have to pay me more
than a lousy 20 wong an hour
to take those things on!
I was only interested
in getting involved
because you said the Kei Pirates
were at the bottom of this one.
It so happens that
guy has the key
to the Kei Pirates and
the Galactic Leyline.
The Galactic Leyline?!
[banging]
Who is it?
[gasps]
Hiya.
[gasps] It's you!
[HARRY]
Open up.
[gasps]
Don't be afraid, I just came
to pick you up, Melfina.
Pick me up?
Great, this toy just
isn't gonna cut it!
[JIM]
Hey, Gene!
What the heck's goin'
on around here?
[GENE] Weren't you
listening in on the radio?
All I got was noise!
I couldn't hear anything!
I guess they jammed
the system somehow.
This is exactly what he's
been planning all along!
Watch my back, Jim, will ya?
[JIM]
You got it!
You're all mine!
What the hell?!
I also have the Space Forces'
top-of-the-line light shield
for protection.
Damn it!
Hey, I got him!
You moron! Do you know
how expensive it is
to get a hold of those
things, Gene?!
[GENE]
This is not the time!
Unfortunately, your light
shield doesn't cut it
against this thing.
I had no idea
you use a Caster.
[HARRY]
Come on! Open up, Melfina!
Come with me, please.
It's for your own good!
Do you hear me?
[screaming]
[HARRY] Why didn't you
open the damn door?
I came here because of you.
Couldn't you at least
show a little gratitude?
I've seen all of your moves.
I suggest you
save your strength.
[yelling]
Stay outta this.
I don't have any
business with you!
[SUZUKA] Now tell us
about the Kei Pirates...
[AISHA] And the mystery
of the Galactic Leyline...
Why don't you just tell us
everything you know?
[chuckles] Sorry,
I don't think so.
What the hell?
Ya know, Casters have
earned the reputation
of being exceptionally effective
against the Tao masters
because they're based on
a totally different
technological system.
This could get ugly...
Two weapons that are using
the same technological system
can defend against each other.
That's a Caster!
Right! And therefore,
we cancel each other out.
[GENE]
This is not good.
I'm gonna run outta
shells before he does.
What's the matter?
You can't run off! I'm not
finished playing with you yet.
Ah, you wanna play?!
Huh?
[GENE]
Getting outta here now!
Where are you going?
Come on! They're after the
Outlaw Star and Melfina!
-- [GENE] What?
--[AISHA, SUZUKA] Huh?
My little brother Harry's
quite taken with Melfina.
[GENE]
Hurry up, Jim!
[JIM]
You got it!
It's 30 minute to the spaceport
no matter how fast they go.
They'll never make it in time.
Hey, wait a minute!
[AISHA]
Hey!
Come back here and
tell me what you know
about the Galactic Leyline!
Tell me what's the matter,
Little Red Riding Hood.
I'm not gonna eat you.
No, don't! Stay away!
Why are you running away?!
I didn't mean to
do that, Melfina.
I'm sorry. I promise
I'm not going to hurt you.
After all, when it really
comes down to it,
we're one and the same.
What do you mean the same?
Yeah, you and I, Melfina.
Both of us,
we're really Constructs.
Constructs? You're one too?
Yes, that's right.
I was born in a test tube,
a human organism made from
synthetic protoplasm.
I was based on
someone else's genes,
but I don't have any parents.
I'm a Construct.
It was just the same
with you, right?
Tell me everything you remember.
I don't know.
I can't remember
anything like that at all.
You've got to remember!
Listen to me, we're
exactly the same.
We're Constructs with greater
abilities than any mere humans.
Nothing good can ever come from
staying with normal people.
Come on. Come with me.
We'll look out for each other.
Come on.
Hey, you can trust me.
No!
[growls]
Why can't I make
you understand?!
I feel so sorry for you.
All these horrible things
have happened to you.
But you can relax now.
I'll protect you,
don't you worry about it.
[screams]
[gasps]
Gilliam, help!
Open up the hatch!
[GILLIAM] What in the
world is the matter?
[yelling]
[GILLIAM yelps]
Open up! Dammit! Open up!
[GILLIAM]
I'm terribly sorry,
but you do not have
the captain's permission
to come aboard.
I don't need
anybody's permission.
[chuckling]
[MELFINA whimpering]
[GILLIAM] Melfina, could you
possibly give me a hand here?
The intruder that has been
pursuing you is trying
to penetrate my protection
from outside somehow.
If something isn't done soon,
he'll be able to
open up the hatch.
Yes, of course.
--[beeping]
--Ah.
[alarm blaring]
[HARRY]
There you are!
I've been looking forward
to meeting you like this.
Now do you believe me, Melfina?
Stop it! Stay away from me!
[HARRY]
Why are you running away?
Why don't you come away with me?
There's no reason to
turn me down, right?
I'm the only one who
can see you like this.
You know it's true, Melfina.
[MELFINA]
Stay away! Stay away!
Hiding in there won't
do you any good.
[MELFINA whimpering]
The truth is, you understand
everything I've said, don't you?
Stay away. Stay away.
There's no place for us around
normal humans anymore.
Haven't you ever felt
left out, unwanted?
Come along with me, Melfina.
You and I belong together,
joined as one forever.
No!
Why?! Why don't you
do what I say?!
What is it? What's your
problem?! What's wrong?
Ah! Stop moving
around by yourself!
[beeping]
[RON]
Harry!
They're on their way.
They'll be coming back soon.
Were you able to get the XGP and
the android like we discussed?
[HARRY] Why doesn't anyone
do what I tell him to do?!
That bitch! My arm's
freaking out!
You mean you blew it?!
Get outta there now, Harry!
[HARRY]
Ah, you son of a bitch!
[RON]
Hm?
[panting]
Ya hear me? Don't you forget!
It's Harry MacDougall
you're dealing with!
I'll catch up to you.
You can count on it!
[GENE]
Melfina! Are you okay?
[GILLIAM]
Don't worry, Gene.
An intruder tried to break
into the main control room
of the Outlaw Star , but
through the valiant efforts
of Melfina and myself,
we drove them off.
Are you sure that
you're okay, Melfina?
Yeah, sure.
I'm really feeling fine, Jim.
Thank goodness. We were
really worried there.
[GENE] The MacDougall Brothers
are on their way after us.
Believe me,
they'll stop at nothing
until they get the
Outlaw Star and Melfina.
I don't think that I can take
too much more of this.
Well, if you can't take
too much more of this,
what do you plan we do?
[GENE]
Good question.
[JIM]
What's this?
It's a message for Mel.
Hi, Melfina. So tell me
how you've been.
Have you been well?
Do you remember me?
It's your friend, Gwen Khan.
Hey! It's that old geezer!
By the way, what're you
still doing on Heifong?
Aren't you going to go look
for the Galactic Leyline?
And he's talkin' about
the Galactic Leylie too.
You have the XGP , but
you still haven't left yet?
Could it be that you don't
have any information?
I see, that must
be it. Right, right.
I've been checking into
things on my end too,
but I haven't uncovered
many clues yet.
Yes, yes. I see, I see.
Well, I'll contact you again.
I'll be in touch if I
find anything further.
That guy still doesn't
make any sense to me.
I know, me either.
But I just figured
something else out.
What's that?
That we really have
no other choice.
We have to go to the Galactic
Leyline at once and end this.
[MELFINA] I can't help but
wonder who he really was anyway.
And... And who am I?
[GENE] With all of my knowledge
and experience with women,
handing out advice about
them is a specialty of mine.
Fred, in your case,
your lack of success
is simply because your body
isn't developed enough
to interest any of these ladies.
Just take a close look
at their powerful bodies
as they face each other in
the ring; they're incredible!
There's a battle
going on between the sexes
and you've got
front row seats!
See it all next time
on Outlaw Star .
Gene Starwind faces off with
"The Strongest Woman
in the Universe"!
You better get ready!