[NARRATOR]
Even in today's world,
where there are weapons
of mass destruction
that can wipe out
an entire planet,
fighters who believe
in only brute strength
and selfless acts of courage,
have not gone completely
out of style.
In every age, survival of
the fittest has been the rule,
no matter how advanced
a civilization might be.
And so, the Universal
Strongman Tournament
was the first competition
created to determine
who was the indisputable
strongest man and woman.
The events cover every
physical challenge imaginable.
Despite strict rules
to protect the lives
of these courageous combatants,
the fights are grueling
and savage to the extreme.
No one has ever in the
history of the tournament
won ten championships in a row.
However, the appearance of one
tough competitor has changed
the course of history for
the tournament forever.
Speed. Stamina.
Technique. Tactics.
And now, this
invincible competitor,
excelling in all of these areas,
has won an unprecedented
four tournaments in a row.
She is called the Ultimate: The
Strongest Woman in the Universe.
[FRED]
So what did you have in mind?
If you wanna borrow more money,
what do I get out of it?
I don't have the time to deal
with chump-change jobs anymore
if that's what
you're talking about.
Look, Fred, this is serious.
You're the only one
I can turn to right now.
[FRED]
Hmm...
Hey, now don't be so formal.
We're closer friends than that.
Have I ever turned you down
for any kind of a favor?
Then you will?
Of course I will.
But only under one condition.
I'm not gonna sleep with ya!
Ha! Please, but I only want
you to do a job for me!
What kinda job?
It'll take place
in just three days.
The annual Galactic
Strongman Tournament,
the biggest event of its kind,
will be held at
the Heifong Coliseum.
It's a no-holds-barred
fight between people
who think they're the
strongest person in the galaxy.
The winner goes home
with the galaxy title
in addition to a purse
of 100 thousand wong.
[GENE] And you're asking me
to enter my name and win it?
Are you crazy?
Your fighting poster boy?
No, that's not what I'm asking.
The problem I have
has to do with the
tournament's female division.
[GENE]
Women fight in this thing, too?
Hey, she's pretty
hot lookin', Fred.
[FRED]
Reiko Ando,
who's held the title of the
Strongest Woman in the Universe
for four years running now.
You gotta be kiddin' me, man.
A cute-looking babe like that?
Huh?
[grunts]
Ah!
I don't care what
you have to do.
Get the job done.
Keep her from winning
a fifth time!
[GENE] Guess I just
don't understand it.
What does it make if
this muscle chick wins
the Strongest Woman in
the Universe title again?
It means that I'll
have to marry her.
[GENE]
Hm?
What did you just say, Fred?
[FRED]
Married.
What do you mean?
What're you tryin' to tell me?
I'm telling you that I'm
gonna have to get married
to that hormonally-challenged
Amazon girl, okay?!
You gotta marry her?
Ugh.
[laughing]
Will ya cut it out, man?
It's no laughing matter.
So why are you making such
a big issue out of all this?
Why not just get married?
Have you completely
lost your mind?
Because I don't want to.
My inquisitive nature
won't be satisfied
until I explore other
amorous pursuits.
Okay. So what does getting
married have to do with
who wins the Strongest Woman
in the Universe tournament?
Luo family tradition says
that the women we select
to be our brides have to be
the strongest in the Universe.
What? What're you
talking about?
Properly speaking, it means
a bride who possesses
mental strength and
a high moral ethic.
But I guess that I
dictated terms to her
that were of a more
general nature.
[GENE]
Hmm...
So ya told her that she
had to win the tournament,
is that what you're saying?
I told her five times!
Five times!
Uh! I figured that she'd
never be able to do it.
But she won.
She has won every year
for the past four years!
Which means that this year
will make it five years running
with you as the prize waiting
for her at the finish line.
I'm gonna smack you if
you don't stop teasing me!
I'm asking you to help me!
Okay, take it easy! But you'll
lend me all of the money
with none of your shenanigans
if I win the tournament, right?
I'll pay the money
in full, as you know.
How's this much sound?
[BOTH chuckle]
Hey, there's no need to be so
formal with me, Freddy boy.
Have I ever once turned
you down for a favor?
Gene.
Okay, my friend, we
have ourselves a deal!
I'm counting on you, Gene!
Do you think you can
handle it, Aisha?
All you have to do
is get in the ring
and defeat that muscle chick.
I'm really depending on you.
Ah, just leave it to me.
It'll be a piece of cake.
I don't care who she is. I can
beat anybody in the galaxy.
The Universe is
a very big place.
I wouldn't be so sure
it'll be all that easy.
For someone as brave
as you are, Suz,
you sure sound like a worrywart.
For the last time, stop
calling me by that name.
Have no fear. Just leave
everything to Aisha!
I've already got a million ideas
how I'm gonna spend
the prize money.
Can't you get this thing
go any faster, Gene?
This girl is ready to rumble!
Why not?! What do
you mean I can't enter?
According to tournament rules,
it states the Ctarl-Ctarl
are not permitted to
enter the competition.
[AISHA]
Why not?
Who made up this stupid rule
that Ctarl-Ctarl aren't allowed
in?! That's discrimination!
F-F-F-Five years ago,
a Ctarl-Ctarl who
qualified as a contestant
in the final tournament
became overly excited
and turned into
some sort of animal.
And then she... pounced on her
opponent, pinning her down,
and bit off her right ear.
[yelps]
No! You're kidding me!
That's not the worst of it.
She was disqualified, but
that made her even more wild.
There were 984 fatalities.
5,379 were seriously wounded.
There were so many people
with wounds, we lost count!
It was a monumental disaster
that was totally unprecedented!
And so, ever since that day,
all Ctarl-Ctarl have been banned
from entering the
tournament, understand?
You can't be serious!
What're we gonna do, Gene?
We haven't got much choice.
If Aisha can't enter,
we haven't got a--
Suzuka.
[SUZUKA grunts]
Are you serious?
You want me to do
a job for Fred Luo?
Right.
Yeah. I just thought...
I didn't think
she'd go for it.
So I guess we're
all out of options.
I know.
[GENE]
Hm?
Why don't you enter
the tournament yourself?
What are you thinking?
I don't have any qualifications.
There's no way I'll
get away with that.
Well, now that's not
entirely true--
Whose side are you on?
Remember I'm a man?
Well now, wait a minute.
That might actually be
an excellent solution.
[GENE]
Huh?
Come on, not you too!
You have number of options.
You just have to
keep an open mind.
[GENE]
Hm?
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and Gentlemen!
Welcome to the 13th annual
Universal Strongman Tournament!
Please welcome Executive
Committee Chairman, Ikki Kazin,
who'll deliver the
opening address!
[IKKI] This message
goes out to all of you
who have entered the Universal
Strongman Tournament.
I want to thank you all
from the bottom of my heart!
And to those 32 women
who have trained so hard
and who have assembled here...
I can't believe it!
Gene Starwind got dressed up
in that embarrassing get-up
just for me!
[grumbles]
[MELFINA] Maybe this color
would look better on you.
[SUZUKA] I think this
would compliment his eyes.
[JIM] We bribed that official,
so don't worry about it.
No one will find ya out.
Now get in there and make
us all some money, Jenny!
[GENE] They were loving
every minute of it.
[IKKI]
Who is the most powerful...
[AISHA] How long does he plan
on rambling on like this?
[GENE] You got that right!
Finish already!
[GENE]
Huh?
[AISHA yawning]
I can hardly keep
awake. Hurry up.
[GENE]
How did she get in here?
[IKKI] ...we will witness the
greatest the world has to offer!
[AISHA]
One. Two. Three. Four.
[GENE] How the hell did you
sneak in here, you animal?
I told you not to call me th--!
Huh?
Gene?
[AISHA laughing]
Ya lose your pom-poms,
little girl?
Well bite me, Aisha!
You are in no position
to laugh at anyone!
Uh? I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm afraid that you're
terribly mistaken.
I'm the mysterious
masked fighter, Firecat.
Any resemblance to Aisha
Clanclan is pure coincidence.
I don't even know her. Ugh!
We can see through
the disguise, Aisha.
I can't believe you fooled them
with that costume, Aisha.
Will you stop calling me Aisha?!
--[clang]
--Huh?
[WOMAN screams]
I tell ya, I'm the
real Firecat! Ah!
[AISHA laughing]
[GENE]
No. You didn't!
I did! Like it or not,
I'm gonna fight as Firecat.
I'll surprise all of you and
win this thing! You'll see.
Hey, wow!
You actually thought things
through for a change!
You're not taking her
side, are you, Jim?
What's the matter? You sound
like you're disappointed
or something, little girl!
This is good news
for you, Gene.
Aisha can fight her instead.
Melfina! Not you, too!
That a girl! I'm gonna
dominate this tournament
and restore the respect
of the Ctarl-Ca--!
[WOMAN screaming]
Hey! Pipe down
in there, will ya?
[sighs] Suit yourself, Aisha.
Please think this
through, Lady Iraga!
If Lord Hazanko
catches wind of this,
there's no telling
what he'll do.
He'll stop at nothing to
make sure that his orders--
Will you shut up?
You think I'm going
to let them choose
who the Strongest Woman
in the Universe is
without me having something
to say about it?
But that's not
we're supposed to!
[IRAGA]
I know that, Tubby.
I'll get them both soon enough.
Victory will be mine, and as
for that idiot, Gene Starwind,
we'll be seeing the last of him.
[ANNOUNCER] The first
match of the first round
in tonight's event
will now begin!
In the blue corner,
representing the Outlaw
brawling style, Jenny Starwind!
And in the red corner,
representing the Ando
comprehensive fighting style,
the Strongest Woman
in the Universe
for four years running,
Reiko Ando!
[CROWD cheering]
[REIKO]
I'll win this tournament.
Nothing in the world can
possibly stop me now.
And I'll go home victorious
after winning the tournament
for a fifth straight time
as Fred's bride!
[shivers]
I felt like someone just
walked over my grave.
Huh?
I'm begging you now, Gene!
Please. You've just
gotta win this one!
[GENE] Hmm. This lady's
built like a rock.
Gene, get in there
and go for it!
Hey! Have you forgotten already?
Don't call him "Gene."
For today you call him "Jenny."
[AISHA]
Oh, that's right!
Ah!
Hey, just what in the world do
you think you're doing, huh?
Although it looks rock-hard,
it's whole lot softer
than you think, Reiko!
[growls]
Knock it off, Jenny. This isn't
the time for that right now.
[GENE]
It's all part of the plan.
[REIKO]
Stand still, damn you!
Can't you get serious?
[GENE]
No! I don't think I can!
He calls this a plan?
He's probably just
trying to confuse her
by throwing her game off,
so he can wear her
down at his own pace.
Their differences in
overall strength is immense.
[giggles] Yoohoo!
Over here! Over he--!
Ge-- I mean, Jenny!
Stop playing around like that!
[REIKO] Ha. What happened to
that terrific plan of yours?
It's working!
By the way, your
breasts feel great!
[growls]
Hey! I think he's
coming around.
Where am I?
The infirmary.
What about the match?
You got your butt kicked, Gene.
How could you humiliate
me in such a way?
What do you propose
I do now? Propose?!
Now look. Just calm
down, all right?
[FRED] How can I be calm
at a time like this?!
We still have an ace
up our sleeves, guys.
I have a geat idea.
[yelling]
[AISHA]
Ganymedian Seaside Upper!
[ANNOUNCER]
And the winner is Firecat!
That's the only trump
card that we have left.
I'm tellin' ya, she's a
hell of the competitor.
Unfortunately, that's
all she's good for.
[AISHA] Triple-reverse
Andromedan Comet Kick!
She did it!
She made it past
the second round!
[bell ringing]
She's good.
I'll give her that much.
[AISHA]
Yeah!
[ANNOUNCER] And the
winner of the first match
of the semifinals is Firecat!
[AISHA laughing]
What a piece of cake that was!
Oh please, Firecat.
Don't let me down now!
You're the only one
that I can count on!
You just leave it to me!
Yeah, just don't get caught with
your tail between your legs.
Well! If it isn't the
delicate Miss Jenny.
The one who got her butt kicked
in the first round of
her very first match.
[GENE grumbles]
The second match of
the semifinals is over!
[GENE]
Oh yeah?
The muscle chick ended up
winning the match, right?
Not exactly.
Reiko lost the match, actually.
Say what?
[MELFINA]
She lost early on.
Nineteen seconds into the match.
It was a quick win for Iraga.
She's a member of the
Hokke Shadow Boxing Team.
That is impossible!
[FRED]
Ohh...
Yeah! I can't believe it!
[FRED laughing]
This is great, Gene!
I don't have to get
married to Reiko!
Yeah. I'm really
glad for ya, Fred.
This is fantastic!
How 'bout we go out
and celebrate!
Now the only thing I need
is to collect my pay.
Your pay?
[GENE]
Uh-huh..
I thought that the
one was to be paid
when the work was
successfully completed,
if I'm not mistaken, Gene.
What exactly was it
that you do to earn it?
Well, I'll be looking forward
to our next encounter.
Until then...
Take care of yourself, Gene!
Fred, wait a minute.
Well, there's really
nothing to discuss, Reiko.
[REIKO]
No, Fred. Don't say that.
I'll start over again,
and train harder than ever.
I'll start trying to win
five in a row next year!
If you have a shred
of compassion,
won't you find it in your heart
to give me another chance?
Oh, well, of course I'll
give you another chance.
But I think you should
consider taking your time
before you start training again.
Whaddya say, Reiko?
That's so nice of you, Fred!
Always worrying like that...
[crack]
[FRED groans]
I love you!
You'll never regret this.
I'll make myself worthy
to be called your wife.
--[crack]
--[FRED yelps, groans]
[ANNOUNCER] The finals
are now ready to begin!
In the red corner,
representing professional
wrestling at its best, Firecat!
Yeah, that's right!
[ANNOUNCER]
And in the blue corner,
representing the Hokke
Shadow Boxing Team, Iraga!
Huh?
[IRAGA] Gene Starwind?
What's he doing here?
Have to stay calm.
The match has to come first.
[AISHA]
I hereby dedicate this match
to the people of
the Ctarl-Ctarl.
I'm gonna win this!
What's the deal? Neither one
of 'em are makin' a move.
I understand that two
experienced fighters
can judge their
opponent's strength
simply by facing each other.
[growls]
[AISHA]
You little--!
Check it out!
She's got her pinned!
Take her out now, Aisha!
[AISHA]
Ha! Oh, yeah!
Uh-oh!
[AISHA screaming]
Hey, Aisha,
pull yourself together.
I thought Ctarl-Ctarl were
supposed to be invincible.
Normally, this is where
I'd let you off the hook
and show a little mercy,
but not if you're one of
Gene Starwind's friends.
You're not leaving alive!
Man, it looks like
she's gonna kill her.
I know!
Even a Ctarl-Ctarl is history
if their head gets smashed in!
Die!
Don't do it!
[yelps]
[chuckles]
[AISHA] You talk too much,
you know that?
You shouldn't say anything
when you're about to
finish someone off.
Damn her. She really had me
worried there for a second.
Don't give an inch,
Firecat! Go for it!
Just leave it to me!
[BOTH yell]
How do ya like that?!
[groaning]
It's all over. Give up, Iraga!
Here it comes.
Yeah, I don't care
how strong she is,
there's no way she can
ever break free--
[BOTH]
Huh?
No way!
If she were faster or smarter,
I can understand,
but how is it she could
be stronger than Aisha?
[AISHA]
Huh?
[CROWD murmuring]
Ya see that?
Guess she's a Ctarl-Ctarl, too!
It's-- It's you!
It doesn't look
like I'll be able
to finish our match right away.
You'll have to take
a rain check.
Sorry. Now I can do my job!
Gene Starwind, take a
last look around you
'cause you are a dead man!
Run, it's a Ctarl-Ctarl!
Let's get the hell out of here!
Who are they, pirates?
Beat it!
Huh?
Here, puppy!
Gene, look out!
I really don't care if
you're a pirate or a wolf.
But I'll be damned if anybody's
gonna stand in the way
of my winning this!
What's that?
Suzuka!
Aisha!
[BOTH]
Suzuka!
I'm all right.
I'm glad to hear it.
But, Gene, what about Aisha?
Uh?
Aisha, can you hear me?!
Where are you?
[SUZUKA]
Gene.
Let's get outta here
while we still can.
We'll be overcome by this
smoke if we don't leave now.
[GENE]
What about Aisha?
Yes, I know.
In her present she-wolf
state of being,
it'll be impossible
to get through to her.
What about Aisha?
Oh no!
[gasps] What is that?
Yeah! Aisha!
She's won the tournament!
That's great!
She did it! She did it!
She's so awesome!
The Ctarl-Ctarl really
are invulnerable.
Maybe I should stop
teasing her for a while.
She really proved herself
to be a champion this time.
[roars]
I can't believe another
Ctarl-Ctarl snuck in the stadium
without even being caught.
You're wrong!
The Ctarl-Ctarl don't run around
with a low-class
wolves like that!
That's an insult!
I've heard the Kei Pirates
have an assassin in their ranks
who turns into a werewolf
when she's provoked.
I bet that was her.
[GENE]
A pirate, huh?
[JIM] More to the point,
what're we gonna do now, Gene?
We didn't get paid, and we've
used up all the bounty we got.
[GENE]
I don't know. My head hurts.
Hello. Starwind and Hawking.
[FRED]
Gene.
[GENE] Oh, it's you.
Whaddaya want, Fred?
[FRED]
Oh, nothing much.
So it sounds like you had a
little trouble after I left.
Listen, Fred,
I'm not in the mood to talk
to you right now, okay?
[FRED]
Wait a minute.
I was just thinking about the
other promise I made to you.
What other promise
are you talkin' about?
I promised I'd lend the money
if you'd agree to take
on the job, remember?
Well, I'm keeping my word.
[GENE]
Really?
I've already filled out
the transfer paperwork
you're going to need.
You should be able to cash
it tomorrow. Is that okay?
That's it for now. Bon voyage!
Thanks, Fred.
So what's up?
--[GENE] Jim.
--Yeah?
We're goin' on a trip.
[MELFINA]
All systems are green.
Launch clearance
has been granted.
Yes! We're finally going
to the Galactic Leyline!
Okay, let's do it!
Outlaw Star , lifting off!
We're on our way!
[GENE]
We've been captured by
a renegade frontier
security agency.
Now they're subjecting Jim and I
to the ultimate humiliation
by putting us on the night watch
for our archenemy, the pirates.
It's really hard to take
orders from someone
who's always barking
at you, ya know?
You gotta relax, Gene. Relax!
Oops, sorry! I guess I
nodded off for a second.
Anyway, next time join us on
Outlaw Star as we explore
"Law and Lawlessness."
You better get ready!