[NARRATOR]
Subject: Jim Hawking.
"Jim" to his friends.
Age: Eleven.
Height: 140 centimeters.
Weight: 32 kilograms.
Blood type: A.
A boy genius, he is the
son of a renowned hacker
known as the
Computer Wizard.
The cautious type, Jim is
Gene Starwind's polar opposite.
Jim always carries a computer
with him and diligently keeps
a close eye on profitable
information and enemy movement.
He is a quick thinker,
yet he is also very
outgoing in his actions.
Jim displays many
precocious traits
which are anything
but child-like.
Although occasionally
victimized and tormented by
Gene's inability to plan ahead,
Jim has not abandoned him.
And judging by the way
he manages Gene,
Jim clearly looks up to him.
[GENE]
Well, that's understandable!
[JIM] Anyway, I'm totally the
kind of guy needed around here
to keep Gene's
bachelor lifestyle
from crashing down
around his ears.
[GENE]
Hey, stop making things up!
Well, that's my cue to leave.
[GILLIAM] I would also like to
ask that you not disturb my job.
[GENE, JIM]
Right!
[GILLIAM]
We are navigating under
uncommonly safe conditions.
There is no unusual
activity to report
outside or inside the ship.
Estimated time of arrival at
Transmit Station Symka 5,
Thirty minutes.
An uneventful trip might
be a bit of welcome relief
to you guys, but it sure
doesn't leave much excitement
for alive-wire
like me, you know.
It could just be a simple
matter of one coincidence
after another, but this is
a weird crew we collected.
Hey! I heard that, Jim.
A child barely out of
diapers like you shouldn't be
insulting a woman who's
mature and worldly!
[JIM grunts]
You heard me?
You better believe it.
The best ears in
the whole universe
are those of the Ctarl-Ctarl.
You won't forget that, right?
No way!
Now that's the good boy, Jim!
Yeah, I think I'm just
beginning to understand
what it really means to
upset you Ctarl-Ctarls.
I wouldn't wanna do that!
[AISHA]
Mm-hm!
That's a sure sign of you
becoming a young man!
Right, whatever you say.
[MELFINA] Jim and Aisha
get along so well.
It's as though
they're really family.
[GENE]
Hm? Family?
[SUZUKA]
Mmm. This tea is delicious.
[computer beeping]
[GILLIAM] I've detected
a ship in the proximity,
and it's rapidly approaching us.
I've made several
attempts to hail it,
but it is not responding
to our signals.
An enemy ship!
[GENE] Why didn't you
spot it earlier?!
[GILLIAM] I can only
surmise that the craft is
utilizing some method to
evade my sensor system.
Or in other words, you're simply
without a clue, right?
--[GILLIAM] Unfortunately.
--[GENE groans]
Uh-oh, Gene, that ship's
almost on our butt!
Go to Grappler combat mode!
[computers beeping]
[GILLIAM] I'm receiving a
signal from the other ship.
[GENE]
Put it through.
[MALE SPACE PIRATE] You're Gene
Starwind of the Outlaw Star?
Nothing personal,
but I'm here to kill you.
It's an enemy ship.
Could that be one of our old
pirate buddies out there?
Probably.
The ship's now within firing
range now, Mister Popular.
Well, let's blow some hot
kisses to my devoted fan.
[JIM]
Launching missiles!
It's a decoy!
Well you bastard,
if it's a grappler fight
you're itchin' for, then you
sure came to right guy!
This punk's not so damn tough.
What the...?!
[FEMALE SPACE PIRATE]
Mata, this guy's a wimp!
[MATA]
C'mon, let's finish him off!
--What the heck's going on?!
--[alarms blaring]
[GILLIAM]
Warning.
Pressure levels are rising
throughout the ship.
If they continue to escalate,
remaining in combat
mode is not advised.
Yeah! I know that!
But these guys are just too
quick and hard to out-maneuver.
The fighting capabilities
of the Outlaw Star
aren't cut out for this.
There is one chance. If I
could only find an opening...
Jim, on my signal, I want ya
to give 'em everything we got!
One last resort, coming up!
Last resort?
[sighs]
That was too close!
So your last resort
was to run away?
What cowards!
Hey, you're alive, aren't you?
Gee, I'd appreciate a
little more gratitude here.
If you consider
that we survived,
then we really haven't lost.
Oh, you two...
[MELFINA] Well, you certainly
make a good team.
Well, Melfina, thanks.
But it's no big deal, ya know.
[laughs]
Somehow it doesn't seem to
me like being called a team
with Gene is so great.
Is that right, James?
What's that supposed mean?
Huh? What do you mean?
[GENE] Seems you and I
need to have a little chat
--about a few things.
--[JIM] Oh no, we don't.
[GENE]
Yes, we do.
[GILLIAM]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we will be arriving at
Symka 5 momentarily.
[JIM] Well, should we go see
about repairs and weaponry?
[GENE]
Yeah.
[MELFINA]
Hey, where's Suzuka?
[AISHA] Suzu mentioned that
she was gonna take a nap.
Yeah, she has a lot of
difficulty working as a team.
Right, maybe, but she's
not the only one!
Well, I don't know
about you guys,
but I'm gonna go
to find some fun!
Another one who can't
just work as a team.
Yeah, like you're
one to talk, Gene.
Yeah, whatever.
You're kidding!
You want me to fix everything
and get you weapons on
a budget like this?
We were hoping that we could
work out a deal of some kind.
If you could do some of
the labor yourselves,
I can give you a discount.
What'll we do?
[GENE]
Like we have a choice.
Go ahead and start
on the repairs for now.
Mister, don't cut
any corners, either.
We can tell you're good
just by looking at
the equipment you've got.
Okay, then.
Fill the paperwork out,
and I'll jump right on it.
All right, thanks!
[GENE] That other ship might
be here on this station, too.
[JIM]
Then shouldn't we look for it?
[GENE] Nah. If they come
at us, I'll take 'em down.
[JIM] Ah! Pretty sure
of yourself, aren't you?
Or maybe you're just lazy?
--[GENE] Say what?!
--[JIM laughs]
You know what I'm saying.
We've got to remember
to keep our guard up.
Right, Gene?
Yeah.
Oh, and one more thing.
I'm gonna go out and party!
Ha. Ha! A couple a'
drinks'll help me unwind!
I'm not kidding, Gene!
I'm really worried about ya!
Come on, lighten up, partner!
I need to have a little fun!
Suit yourself! Melfina, would
you please tag-a-long with this
idiot here and keep
him out of trouble?
Sure!
Wh-What? Wait a minute!
I was talking about
going out alone!
Bang!
What did I do to desrve this?
Ya wany anythin'else?
Oh, this dessert is
plenty for me, thank you.
Yup. That's great.
Glad to hear it, Melfina.
[sighs]
[typing]
[JIM] How come I'm always
the one who gets stuck
doing everything around here?
[GILLIAM]
It's rough, isn't it, Jim?
Hey, thanks a lot, Gilliam.
Ya know, you're the only
one who ever notices
how much I bust my butt?
[GILLIAM] I have the combat
data on the enemy vessel.
Without a strategy, we're not
gonna beat that other ship.
Gene never plans ahead,
he makes it up as he goes.
But this time,
it's all up to me.
[GILLIAM] Shall I brew a
pot of coffee for you?
Sure. Sounds great!
[typing]
[yawns]
[GILLIAM]
Jim, it's already morning.
Perhaps you should take a break.
Man, I'm exhausted,
but I can't go to bed yet.
Guess breath of fresh
air might do me good.
[JIM whistling]
[cat meows]
[JIM]
Hm? Wha...?
Huh. Wow! You don't see
many cats on space stations.
[Jim grunts]
Hey! C'mere little kitty.
--[Cat meows]
--Psst. Psst.
--[JIM] Oh...
--[cat meows]
--[JIM giggles]
[JIM]
Aw. That's a good kitty cat.
[JIM chuckles]
[JIM]
Aw. There you go!
Boy, you guys
really like it, huh?
Huh?
Hey! Wait a minute, guys!
Don't you wanna play some more?
[JIM]
Huh? Hmm...
Here kitty, kitty, kitty.
[JIM]
Oh...
[GIRL sighs]
[Jim]
Hmm...
[GIRL]
Hm? Hmm...
Hi.
Are those your kitty cats?
They are.
Why do you want to know?
Uh...?! Um...
No reason, just wondering.
Just wondering?
M-Maybe I was just
trying to talk to you?
Is that all right?
[GIRL] Why? Do you
like me or something?
[JIM] N-No, I didn't
mean it like that!
Well, maybe I do.
[GIRL]
Hm?
So do you live
here on the station?
Oh, no. Just passing
through on a trip.
--[JIM] Hm. So you're traveling
--[cat meowing]
with your cats?
Yeah, this is Mata and Kemi.
So, what's your name?
Oh, sorry.
My name's Hanmyo.
My name's Jim Hawking.
I'm on a trip, too.
I just stopped off here at
the station for a while.
[HANMYO]
Hm?
Oh, wow! Then it's fate!
Huh?!
Don't you see? We were
supposed to meet!
What are the chances that both
our ships would stop here?
It was fate, Jim!
Fate...?
I guess so.
[meowing]
[HANMYO] Well, I have to go
back and feed the kitties, now.
[JIM]
Mm. Uh... Well...
Can you come back
again this afternoon?
Okay!
Great! I'll meet you
here at one o'clock!
[HANMYO]
Well then! See you later!
Bye!
[JIM sighs]
[MELFINA]
Jim, more coffee?
Yeah, thanks.
So where's Gene?
Still sleeping.
He drank an awful lot
of liquor yesterday.
But, Melfina. What went wrong?
You were supposed to
keep an eye on him.
Yes. I tried to stop him.
But when I did, he started
drinking even more.
[JIM grunts]
Sounds like Gene.
[GENE]
What does?
[JIM scoffs]
Good morning, sunshine.
[groans]
There's an inspirational image.
Okay, hurry up and eat now,
we've got a busy day.
Yeah, yeah.
[yawns]
Hey, how's it coming, mister?
Doing just fine,
considering I'm not making
any profit on this job.
But it's a great ship.
I've never seen this model out
here on the frontier before.
Nice one, huh?
[SHOP OWNER]
Yeah, she's a real beauty.
[JIM]
Good work! Keep it up!
[SHOP OWNER]
Leave it to me!
[JIM] Hey there,
how's it coming along?
Look, I know that we're cutting
back on costs. However,
you could offer a little bit of
help with the workload here.
This isn't a run-of-the-mill
fix it job.
What the hell's the big idea?
You're making me change out
the arms' wiring on this thing!
That's a lot of work!
Look, Gene Starwind!
Don't you hear that voice
deep inside you telling you
to work harder in order
to pay for the bar tab
you racked up yesterday?!
[chuckles]
Yes, I was so wrong.
What was I thinking?
Please, Master James, what more
can this unworthy
servant do for ya?
Well, if you were
on a first date,
what kind of present
would ya bring?
What's wrong?
Has my little Jimmy
discovered girls?
[laughs]
All right!
This is your first step
toward being a man,
so feel free to ask the
pro anything you want.
Aw, forget it!
I'm an idiot to ask advice
from a lech like you!
Not all guys have only one
thing on the mind, sleazeball!
Hey, watch it, you little runt!
Now you're really
ticking me off.
You're dirty, slimy, and scumy!
--Thats it, c'mere.
--[JIM grumbles]
[GILLIAM]
Oh, dear, how embarrassing.
[HANMYO]
Guess who?!
Hanmyo!
[HANMYO giggles]
That's right!
Um...
Here.
You brought me flowers?
[giggles]
Wow!
[JIM]
Uh...!
That is so nice.
[nervous chuckles]
[MELFINA]
The X-axis checks out normal.
[GENE] There's less
damage than I thought.
[MELFINA]
Good news, isn't it?
Yeah. The Outlaw
Star 's one of a kind.
It really is a fine ship.
[GENE]
Huh?
Huh? What is it, what's wrong?
Uh, what do you mean?
There's nothing wrong.
Gene?
I said it's nothing!
Am I...
...in the way?
No, of course you're not.
God, it's not that at all!
We need you here, Melfina.
[MELFINA]
All right.
[computer beeps]
[GILLIAM]
Please pardon the interruption,
but a video mail transmission
has just been received
from Fred Luo.
[GENE]
Play it.
Gene, my old friend, how are
you and your merry troupe
doing out there at your
end of the universe?
These messages are expensive,
so I'll keep it short.
I have news about an
interesting place that's
related to the Galactic Leyline.
I mailed the details to
Jim in an encoded file.
Well, good luck.
Take care of yourselves, now.
[GILLIAM]
End of message.
We'll have to check
out the place.
Things are sure beginning
to liven up around here.
[AISHA] I can already
smell the treasure!
Let's get going!
Don't you ever knock?
[meows]
[HANMYO]
That was fun, huh?
[JIM]
Yeah.
Hey, do ya think we could
meet again tomorrow?
Oh, yes!
We can meet right here at
the same time we met today!
Okay, then I'll be here.
Me, too.
[giggles]
[HANMYO]
Jim?
[JIM]
Yeah?
[HANMYO]
Thanks for the flowers.
I've never gotten any before.
[JIM]
You're welcome. See ya!
[HANMYO]
Bye-bye!
[KEMI] Hanmyo, you haven't
forgotten about our mission,
have you?
[MATA] Yes, that's right.
You haven't, have you?
Will you stop worrying?
All I have to do is
disable their ship
and get rid of Gene Starwind.
[MATA]
Okay, okay.
The Outlaw Star
hasn't launched yet.
[KEMI] Hanmyo, I wish you hadn't
made another date like that.
You should've discussed
it with me first.
[MATA]
And me as well.
Well I'm sorry,
but this is fate.
Don't worry about it.
I will finish the job.
[MELFINA]
All systems green.
All right, people. Let's launch.
What's wrong, Jim? You seem
kinda down in the dumps.
Oh, right, I forgot.
How'd your big date turn out?
It went just great, as if
it's any of your bee's wax,
so back off! Now let's
get outta here!
[JIM] I'm sorry, Hanmyo.
I can't make it.
[GILLIAM]
Alert!
A solitary vessel is closing
in on our ship from astern.
[AISHA]
What's he up to?
Oh, he's taking his time.
Just like a feline
toying with a mouse.
Looks like he's trying
to screw around with us.
Well then, we're just
gonna have to show him
what a mouse can do
when it gets cornered.
Jim, what course of action
would you recommend?
"There's more than one way to
skin a cat," as the saying goes.
What a vile saying!
Don't take it personally, Aisha.
Going to Grappler combat mode!
[KEMI]
Roger.
[MATA]
Ready when you are.
[KEMI]
Same here.
[HANMYO]
Let's finish him off quick.
I have an appointment to keep.
[MATA]
Focus.
[KEMI]
Relax.
I am relaxed, don't worry.
I can sense the power.
It's coming now.
[GENE]
Is this really gonna work?
[JIM]
I dunno.
But if we do it the same
as last time, we'll lose.
[GENE]
Yeah. Probably.
[JIM]
Gilliam!
Cut all external monitors
except this one.
And stand by to activate.
Gene, you concentrate
on piloting.
I'll back you up
without your instructions.
The Arms' response
has been increased
to 150 percent.
Aisha, Suzuka they're all yours.
Hey, this is easy!
It's like a game!
Yeah, well keep in mind there's
no reset button on this game.
[GILLIAM] This system can
only remain operational
for one minute. Keep alert
and be careful, everyone.
And good luck to you.
[MELFINA] Let's all pull
together the way a team should.
If anybody can do it, we can.
Gosh, I feel like crying.
[GENE]
Let's do it!
[KEMI]
He's pinned!
Bastard!
[JIM]
He's making another pass!
[growls]
[shouts]
[AISHA]
Now!
[KEMI screams]
[MATA]
They killed Kemi!
They're gonna get it!
[MATA grunts]
I think I'm beginning to
get the hang of it now.
[HANMYO]
Let go of Mata!
[JIM]
Launching all missiles!
[MATA grunts]
[MATA screams]
[HANYMO]
Mata!
Oh, no!
[ALL shout]
Did we get him?
A dead ship.
The Torarato won't respond.
Kemi... Mata...
Yeah!
[GILLIAM] Although the
adversary is defeated,
we sustained extensive
damage as well.
Then we have no choice.
We'll have to return to
Symka 5 for more repair.
Now what about cash?
[JIM]
Don't sweat it!
We'll figure out something.
[GENE]
What're you so happy about?
Me!
Uh... No reason.
[chuckles]
[inaudible]
[AISHA] We're off to the
Leyline and the treasure!
It must be nice to
be a Ctarl-Ctarl
without any problems.
That isn't true.
A delicate flower such as
I has her share of concerns.
Like what?
Well...
Uh...
I get hungry.
[sighs]
[JIM] You call that
a concern? Gimme a break!
[AISHA] Well then, okay,
what would you call a problem?
[JIM] The big stuff, like,
"What do people exist for"?
"What's in my heart"?
"Who am I"? That's what!
[AISHA]
You need a life.
[JIM]
You just don't get it!
[GENE] In our next episode,
the secret of the Galactic
Leyline is gonna be revealed
among the ancient ruins
of a mysterious planet!
Now I'm not trying to
be cocky or anything,
but story development has
to follow a certain order,
ya know.
I can't just blurt the
whole plot out to ya.
What?
You wanna find out now?
All right.
Believe it or not,
the Leyline is really...
Well, to tell ya the truth,
I don't know what
the secret is, either.
Next time on Outlaw Star:
"Grave of the Dragon"!
You'd better get ready!