[NARRATOR]
To kill.
That is this woman's profession.
That is the only means
by which she can survive.
Her name is Suzuka.
There are none
who know her past.
There are none who
ask about her past.
Through killing,
she finds herself.
She weeps as she
watches the wind,
and senses the currents of
the universe in her skin.
This is the kind of
woman that Suzuka is.
She is not a special woman.
All woman are special.
All woman possess many faces.
Yet, no man has ever seen
the faces of Suzuka.
All that men can see
is the gleaming sword
she holds in her hands.
Even if these men, who
see her gleaming blade,
were to receive
just a brief smile,
they would never see it nor know
of it while they were alive.
This woman's name is Suzuka.
To kill.
This is her profession.
[CONTROL MAN]
Don't be stupid!
Start your landing approach!
[GENE] I don't have the fuel!
I'm comin' in!
[CONTROL MAN]
Decelerate!
You gotta cut down your speed!
Follow the guide beacon!
That's what I'm doing!
[CONTROL MAN]
There's no wind today!
What kind of landing
is he trying to pull?!
[GENE] Hey, I haven't piloted
a spaceship in six years!
And my dad never taught
me how to make planetfall,
so this is the first time
I've ever landed one!
Oh, great.
Any other suprises
you got for us?
[MELFINA]
I'll handle alignment
with the landing
beacon from here.
[GILLIAM] Why don't you take
care of the whole procedure
from this moment on, Melfina?
[MELFINA] I can't take care
of the whole procedure.
Hey! It's my ship!
And I'll do it!
I hate to say it but, we're
still comin' in too fast!
Ahh... Come on!
Hey, how 'bout that?
[GILLIAM]
That is a problem.
[GENE]
Mm? Ugh?!
[JIM]
Gene!
[GENE]
Shit!
[MELFINA]
One hundred to surface.
Deploy landing struts.
I'm on it!
[GILLIAM]
Easy, Gene. Be gentle now.
Ah, sue me!
[JIM]
I'm hatin' this! Ah!
Dammit! [grunting]
[MELFINA]
Please cut the engines.
I'll get us under control.
[GILLIAM] Landing strut
three status is yellow.
It's going to break,
at this rate.
Lay off! This ship isn't that
flimsy, and you know it!
[GENE, JIM sigh]
[CONTROL MAN]
Outlaw Star ...
Welcome to Sentinel III,
West Virginia Spaceport.
Yeah, I pulled it off, no prob.
[JIM]
What are you talking about?!
You almost got us killed!
[GILLIAM] With this captain's
piloting technique,
I worry about my
future prospects...
Ha!
[CONTROL MAN]
So, what'll it be?
Will you be taking off
once you're re-supplied
or do you plan to park
here for while?
[GENE]
Take us to the cheapest dock.
We may be registered
out of Blue Heaven,
but our crew is from here.
So, what do you wanna do, Gene?
Go back to the shop?
No, I want to go to Fred Luo's
place over in Hugo right away,
but before that I'd like to
know what happened to our car?
Ah!
It's been sitting in that silo!
Yeah, I wonder if
it's been stolen?
No way, it can't be!
Ahh, let's just rent a
car for now so we can
get over to Hugo.
We can make it in three
hours if we hurry.
Aw. I sure hope my Ehefrau's
okay, after all this time.
Okay.
Once we've taken care of
business, we'll go look for it.
[JIM] All right, but I don't
know how to act around that guy.
Come on, Jim. You think
I know any better?
[FRED]
Oh, Gene!
It's been so long!
[GENE]
You're looking well, Fred.
[FRED] You never call me!
You never write me!
I never hear from you. Aw!
I'm so very happy
you came to see me!
[GENE]
Y-Yeah, I-I'm happy, too.
Is this Gene's friend Fred Luo?
Yeah, that'd be him. Gene did
some job for him awhile ago.
Oh, is that you James?!
It looks like you're
growing up quickly!
Yeah, well, I guess.
[sighs]
Yeah, yeah, okay. It's nice
to see you, too, Fred.
[FRED]
I can't wait to see you
in another two or three years.
Yeah, well in two
or three years,
I think I'll be some
place far, far away.
[FRED] Well then,
I'd just come after you,
to the edge of the
universe if I had to.
And who might this
young lady be?
Uh...
Uh. How do you do?
My name is Melfina.
Yes, pleased to meet you.
Fred, I have some business
to discuss with you.
Man, It's a good thing
you're here on Sentinel
and I found you.
Yeah, my father secured
our company's headquarters
on Heifong.
Now that I'm in charge,
I want to concentrate my
efforts on the frontier.
If I don't expand
the Luo family's market
beyond what my dad has,
I'll be a laughing-stock.
And what's goin' on with Earth?
[FRED]
Well, the Federation merchants
are pretty powerful there.
So, what's this business
you mentioned, huh?
It's my spaceship.
I'm gonna need a--
--[FRED exhales]
--[GENE screams]
[FRED]
It was just a joke! A joke!
[panting]
[GENE] Come on, man, I thought
I told you that I hate
those jokes of yours, Fred!
Okay, okay! No more
jokes, all right?
Yeah, right.
I'll be series from now on.
[GENE] It's even worse
when you're series.
Com'on, I'm not kidding.
So, you were saying something
about a spaceship?
That's right, I finally
got my hands on one.
[FRED]
Well, that's great!
You know, Gene, you should have
gone into space a long time ago!
[GENE]
I know.
But, the ship doesn't have
any equipment or weapons.
I want you to sell me some.
[FRED] Gene, we may be friends,
but business is business.
Do you have any idea how much
weapons and equipment costs?
Yeah, I know, I know,
but I'm not too sure what
the situation is on this one.
I have a Grappler Ship.
Ohh... You know we have
a rule in the Luo family
to never to ask
the customer "why."
That means we sell the
customer what they want,
no questions asked.
But for the first time in my
life, I want to break the rules.
I don't know, Fred.
I don't know if you
should break that rule.
Oh, dear, it's even more
expensive with a Grappler Ship.
And we can't go through
our legitimate routes.
But, I think I will be able to
help you with the equipment,
except when are
you gonna pay me?
When I make it big!
Gene, we have another
rule in the Luo family:
Trust can't be
bought with money,
but it can't take
it's place either.
Trusting you and knowing
I'll be paid by you
are two different
things all together.
Now, that rule you
can break, all right?
Come on, Gene, you know
you can't do business
without some assurance
you'll be paid.
Look, I'll write
out what I want,
so could you at least
give me an estimate?
[FRED]
I suppose.
But after you've seen
the price on the estimate
you may have a change of heart.
Use the desk in
the display area.
It's time for my
next appointment.
All right, then.
Hey, you!
[GENE]
Hm?
Do you know why we don't turn
you away and lock you out
even though you're rude
to the young master?
Uh. Cause you'll get yourself
hurt if you take me on?
No. Because the young master
happens to love you.
[GENE]
What was that?
[JIM]
I don't wanna know.
Damn, he's more tight-fisted
than I thought it was.
[JIM]
That's how people operate, Gene.
Hey, aren't you gonna
put together that list
for an estimate?
Oh, yeah, right.
[FRED]
Welcome, young lady.
I see you were
referred by Mr. Oh.
You need large quantities
of military rifles, then?
[WOMAN]
No, I don't want any rifles.
Excuse me? What do
you want, then?
And the referral from
Mr. Oh is a lie, as well.
What I want, Mr. Luo,
is your life.
[FRED]
Huh?!
I'll let you to live...
...for just another five
minutes. You may feel free
to take the time to write
out a farewell letter
to say your goodbyes.
However, should you
not accept your death
under these terms,
you will die at once.
Why is that you're after me?
If you continue to
expand your market,
someone else's is
bound to shrink.
Some people find
that unacceptable.
Is it Ralph? Or is it Otto?
Who could it be?
You have four minutes.
The sun will soon drift
below the horizon.
After all, that is a
fitting time to die.
I... can't believe it!
You're "Twilight" Suzuka?!
Introductions are a bit late,
don't you think you should
put better use to what
little time you have left.
[gasping]
[SUZUKA]
Is something the matter?
You have only three minutes.
Hey, Fred!
[GENE grunting]
A light shield, huh?
Gene! I'm over here!
Save me! Save me!
Help me, Gene!
[GENE]
Stay down!
[FRED]
Ah! [whimpers]
Agh!
[GENE]
I have a light shield, too.
[SUZUKA]
Heh.
[GENE grunting]
[SUZUKA]
I won't tolerate interference.
Okay, whaddya say we play fair?
Charming...
Do you actually think
that your using a sword
would be challenging?
[GENE yelling]
[ringing]
[gasps]
What's that?
It's too late,
I failed to kill him!
[SUZUKA yells]
[GENE groaning]
I'm okay, Gene!
[SUZUKA]
Fred Luo!
I'll wait for your life!
Just until the next sunset.
Damn! She knows how
to make a fast exit!
[FRED]
Aw! Gene! You saved my life!
You have to keep on protecting
me until this is all over!
So, you want me to do
something about her, huh?
I'll take the job, but only if
you do something about this.
[FRED]
Huh?
If this is all you need,
it's a bargain!
Huh What?
[FRED]
You don't understand...
No one has ever been targeted
by "Twilight" Suzuka and lived.
She's an ultra-class-A assassin.
Oh, yeah...
What may I ask are you doing?
I'm adding in some more missiles
that I was holding back on.
[FRED]
Huh?
First, I must deal
with that bodyguard.
[BODYGUARD A] It doesn't seem
to be a sensor malfunction.
But the sensor didn't
pick up anything at all,
I don't understand.
[GENE]
It was a Bokuto.
It's a sword made of wood.
It would never be picked
up by the sensors.
A wooden sword?
Are you saying she did this
with a wooden sword?
[GENE]
That's exactly what I'm saying.
Hey Fred, you got any
Caster shells around here?
There's little demand for them.
Plus they're antiques and that's
just not our style around here.
[GENE]
So, what're you gonna do?
What am I gonna do?
Yeah, are you gonna just wait
for her to show up again,
or are you gonna get
the hell out of here?
Well, she did tell you you
had till the next sunset.
[GENE] People like that
always stick to their style.
And you can bet they'll go after
anyone who interferes with it.
And since, you interfered,
I guess she's goin' after ya.
Uh... Oh, shit!
Wait a minute here,
let me think things over.
There's got to be
a way out of this.
I've got it!
Why not track down her employer
and kill him first?!
Assuming we can find him
before the next sunset,
which is 23 hours from now.
Well, guys, let's get goin'!
Huh? But where are we going?
I'm tired. I want to find
a hotel and get some rest.
But you can't, Gene!
You've gotta stay with me,
you can't leave!
If you need a place to stay,
you can use my room!
Stay with me wherever I am,
in my bed or in the bath!
Thanks a lot Fred,
but I'll pass!
Don't worry, she'll
stay true to her word.
See ya!
[FRED]
But! But, Gene...
[GENE] I'll give you a call,
once we find a hotel!
[door clicks]
[whimpers]
[JIM] Hey, are you really
gonna be his bodyguard?
[GENE]
Like I have a choice.
Look Jim, you know
that the Outlaw Star
needs a whole mess of supplies.
If he says I can't pay
him when I make it big--
[SUZUKA]
That is no longer a possibility.
I am "Twilight" Suzuka.
Shall we not waste anymore
time and begin our duel?
I'm Gene Starwind.
I'm sorry to disappointed you,
but dueling isn't
an Outlaw custom.
[SUZUKA] Once the opponents
have named themselves,
the fight has begun!
What?! You've gotta
be kidding me!
Melfina!
Go back to Fred's place!
[JIM]
What about me?!
[GENE]
Back me up!
[JIM]
No way!
[GENE]
Great.
Damn! My gun is useless.
[GENE]
That was great!
Was that one of those tricks
that only masters can do?
That was merely
a feat of strength.
Secret techniques
aren't necessary
against those who runs away.
Heh, heh! You hurt
my feelings.
[SUZUKA] Why don't you stop
running and learn to face me?
Gene! Get in!
[GENE]
See ya later!
You can't get away!
[JIM]
Gene! She's following us!
Damn, that lady's persistent.
Looks like I'm gonna
have to take her on.
Jim, listen, while
we're on the road,
I'll need you to do
something for me.
[SUZUKA] Have you finally
decided to face me in a duel?
You know, I gotta do
something about you,
otherwise I'm not gonna
get what I want from Fred.
[SUZUKA]
Worldly desires are foolish.
They have cost you your life.
Perhaps, and there are some
desires that are big enough
to risk your life for!
This is one of them!
I have to put my life
on the line for this!
What are you up to now?
[GENE]
Get down here!
What's the matter?
Are you scared?
You fool!
[SUZUKA yells]
A shield?
If you focus 'em at a single
point, then you can do this!
You need to know
the trick to it.
That won't work!
[SUZUKA chuckles]
Dammit!
Come back here!
[SUZUKA gasping]
[GENE]
I got it!
Give that to me!
Which one?!
[SUZUKA]
Both of them!
[GENE]
Hmm?
[sniffing]
Stop that! What do you
think you're doing?!
This smells real nice.
That's a beautiful
woman for ya.
Will you stop fooling around!
[GENE] If you want your
sash and sword back,
I suggest you let Fred Luo live.
I plan on carrying
out my contract.
Then, I won't give them
back. The sash will go
in my collection, and
I'll just break the sword.
[SUZUKA] You can't!
I won't let you do that!
[GENE] Like you can
do anything about it!
Damn you!
Yeah, I don't wanna
hear it anymore!
We're makin' a deal right
now, a deal on my terms,
a draw and nothing more.
Anything but a draw!
If I'd used a secret
technique first,
this wouldn't 've happened!
Can't ya handle it?
Then fine. You lost.
You underestimated me.
I lost?
I can't.
If it were just a fight
between you and me,
there wouldn't be a problem.
But I don't stand a chance
fighting over Fred's life.
I can't stay with Fred
and protect him
for the rest of my life.
I'm going back into space.
You mean to tell me you're not
his bodyguard after all of this?
[GENE] No, I told you
right from the start.
I'm an Outlaw.
Outlaw?
That's right.
I will carry out my contract.
I'll keep trying
as long as I live.
I still have my pride.
Then you will die!
[GENE]
"Twilight" Suzuka just died.
[SUZUKA gasps]
Forget about your contract.
[SUZUKA]
Flawed reasoning like that
will not convince me to give up!
[GENE]
Well, works for me.
Here, you can have these back
as payment for Fred's life.
Wait! You must understand
I cannot consent
to deal like that!
[GENE]
Why?
Because you're bound
by a contract?
[SUZUKA]
No, by my pride.
[GENE]
Well then.
I guess I'm the one who's
damaged your pride.
So, how 'bout we try
and make another deal?
If you're going to kill Fred,
then you have to kill me first.
Yes, that goes without saying.
[GENE]
Great! We have a deal, then!
On your pride now, don't
forget what you said.
What?!
But, I uh...
[GENE] I'll be careful
during sunsets, okay?
But...
Oh, right...
Okay! That settles it that then!
Gene, are you sure that's
a good idea, saying that?
There is not much else I can
say, Jim, protecting myself
is gonna be a lot of easier
than me protecting Fred.
Okay, fine, whatever you say.
[SUZUKA]
That man... Why...?
[FRED]
So, I should deliver them
to dock 26 at Locus'
spaceport, then?
[GENE]
Yeah. Thanks.
I knew that I could
count on you, Gene,
you have truly saved my life!
"Twilight" Suzuka won't be
coming after me anymore, right?
Yeah, but I'm not so sure
about the guy who hired her.
Well, I can handle that.
Given enough time,
I'll be able to find him.
Well, I hope to get more help
from you in the future.
Let's just say you owe me
for getting Suzuka
to want to kill me.
[FRED] What I owe you comes
to 750 thousand wong.
What are you talking about?
[FRED] That's what left
when you subtract
the cost of the
items you ordered
from how much it would
cost you to hire Suzuka!
Damn it, Fred!
Hey, you guys, I thought
you said he loved me?!
The young master gave
you a 30% discount.
[BODYGUARD B]
Hm-hm!
[FRED]
That's right, Gene, a discount!
[GENE]
Huh?! Ah!
Aw! I look forward to
a long relationship!
It costs a lot to
maintain a spaceship!
Even more so with a
Grappler Ship, you know!
[sighs] Yeah, Fred, I know.
These damn merchants.
That's it. The
negotiations are over.
Oh, I see.
Gene, do you think you persuaded
that assassin woman to give up?
I wouldn't call it
"persuaded," exactly.
Hey! I couldn't just
kill her! So sue me!
Yeah, yeah...
[MELFINA]
Oh?
[SUZUKA]
Gene Starwind,
this isn't over.
[GENE]
I got a ship and I got a woman.
Now I can live out the rest
of my days in peace,
but I don't think
that's gonna happen.
Those damn pirates
are attacking again!
And these new guys
are real tough!
They're makin' it
hard for all of us!
Go, Suzuka!
Stand up to 'em, Jim!
Given the situation, I guess
I better get outta there, too.
They can't do it without me.
Next time, on Outlaw Star :
"Creeping Evil"!
You better get ready!