[NARRATOR]
They kill as well.
If it'll make them
some money, that is.
Pirates? Outlaws?
Space Forces flunkies?
No, they're none of those.
But they'll take
jobs from anyone.
Right. If it'll make
them some money.
At any rate,
they're like hyenas who are
valued by all the powers.
They're dangerous if
you get too close to them.
And they're good.
If they weren't,
somebody would've shot
them in the back long ago.
They are more powerful than
other people's hatred of them.
Everyone in the
underworld knows the name,
"The MacDougall Brothers."
But no one knows what
the MacDougall Brothers
are really like.
They're careful, bold, cunning,
and will do anything for money.
They're dependable,
tough, ruthless.
Everyone who knows anything
more than just rumors
has been killed.
Yeah.
All at the hands of the
MacDougall Brothers.
[MELFINA] Distance to border
of Lione Lagrange Point,
30,000 kilometers.
Jim, do ya see any
sign of the El Dorado ?
Nope, still nothing.
But the magnetic storm seems
to be affecting the sensors
just a little.
[GILLIAM]
According to the findings
on the latest
meteorological data,
it appears as though solar
flares are still active.
This magnetic storm will
probably last a while.
Good. That means they're
in the same situation.
And now it's payback
time, El Dorado .
[GENE]
What did you say?
What do you mean the El Dorado
has dropped out? Huh?
[STAFF C]
You're askin' the wrong guy.
[GENE]
Where did he go?
Tell me!
Well, sir... that's just it.
We have a comm cube
with your name on it.
It was sent directly
from the El Dorado .
What? Sent to me?
[MELFINA] Distance to
LaGrange Point, ten thousand.
[GILLIAM]
Still no sign of the enemy.
Gene, wouldn't he be inside
the asteroid field by now?
More than likely, but I
don't wanna go in there yet
until I'm absolutely certain.
I'm slowin' us down.
[HARRY] I'm fed up with that
so-called luck of yours.
You're wasting my time.
Come over to the Lione LaGrange
Point. I wanna finish this.
Make it within 50 hours.
If you get there before me,
I'll tell you whatever
you wanna know.
Whaddya think?
I guess that he's
challenging us to a duel.
Interesting.
[GILLIAM] Oh, my. Collected
interplanetary material.
Sudden ether current
interference. Magnetic storms.
Horrible conditions.
It doesn't look like radar,
CFS, or subspace radar
are gonna be of any use
to us in this region.
So we'll just have to rely
on our eyes, that's all.
Then leave it to me
'cause I got the eyes!
Yeah.
I hear that the Ctarl-Ctarl
have got the best eyes around.
Just give me one good reason
why we have to bring you along.
You're the ones who
ruined my chances
of moving up in the world.
Hmph!
You're gonna make of for it!
I have to find the
Galactic Leyline
and you're gonna
help me do it now!
Okay, but there is something
I've been wanting to ask you.
Just what in the hell
is the Galactic Leyline?
[AISHA]
What?! You don't even know that?
Hilda didn't exactly
divulge information.
Well, listen closely.
At the Galactic Leyline,
there's an incredible treasure.
Treasure? Like what?
Some kindaf precious metal?
That or a storehouse
of Dragonite.
In other words, the Empire's
intelligence bureau
estimates that it's value
is capable of buying
an entire solar system!
Wow! Totally cool!
However "cool" it is,
it's just a thing.
From just the little
bit I have heard,
I wouldn't go so far as to call
it some incredible treasure.
What would you call it?
A gate.
I don't know. I hear that
it's some kind of gateway.
Then that's it!
That gateway is probably
made outta Dragonite.
That will make sense to me!
Anyhow, there's absolutely no
way we can't take you with us.
This is our own duel, okay?
Uh, uh, uh...
If these MacDougall
Brothers know something
about the Galactic Leyline,
then I'm definitely
coming along with you guys.
Do you understand
what I've said to you?!
[AISHA]
Hmm...
I don't see any sign of them.
[JIM]
Maybe it's a trap.
[GENE] Of course it's
a trap. Whaddya think?
They wanna destroy this ship.
That is, the ship
called the XGP .
[JIM, AISHA]
Huh?
One moment. A moment
please, gentlemen.
Huh? You mean us?
Yes, that's right.
I'm addressing you.
How did you come into
possession of that ship?
Mh-hm. That ship.
So, who are you?
[chuckles]
I'm Gwen Khan. Yes, I'm Gwen.
I am a race official.
Of this race.
Mh-hm. That's what
I am, an official.
And what exactly what
makes you so interested
in our ship, Mr. Official?
I'm interested.
Yes, interested.
Yes, I am.
It's a high-performance ship
made by an unknown manufacturer.
Yes, it's a high-performance
ship, it truly is.
Is that so?
[JIM]
Mhm.
Come now, tell, do tell.
How did you come by
that ship, I must know.
That is the mystery.
Yes, that is the mystery.
[GENE]
Hm...
We found it.
Found it?
Hm... You found it?
Is that possible? No!
How odd. You found it?
Yep! It was abandoned
and without an owner.
So I guess that means
it's our ship now.
Is that a problem?
A problem?
A problem.
Let's see,
I suppose there isn't.
No. No problem at all.
[GENE]
Good!
All right then.
You'll have to excuse us
'cause we're in a hurry.
[KHAN]
Gentlemen!
Are you guys going to re--?
[GENE]
What?
[click]
[chuckles]
it's nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
Nothing. Nothing.
I'm just so bored.
What was the deal with
that old man, Khan?
I don't know.
By the way, Gene,
are we just gonna
keep on circling this
asteroid field forever?
Ehh, we can't find
our dance partner
so what choice do we have?
Hey, maybe I'll just
slow down a little bit.
[MELFINA] All engines
systems show green.
Green is good.
Now what about Newton
reactors 1 and 3?
[MELFINA]
Functioning normally.
[GILLIAM]
Well, yes, of course.
Although it may have
been a rush job,
the repairs have been completed.
Gee, your superiority,
once again, saves the day.
[GILLIAM]
Your praise flatters me, Gene.
One moment.
Now what?
[GILLIAM]
Detecting missiles closing in
from nine o'clock high.
[GENE]
Missiles? With no warning?
Enemy ship spotted ahead!
This'll be a one-on-one duel.
That isn't a problem, is it?
Now, now, this
isn't exactly fair.
It's pretty obvious that
you intend to destroy us,
but there's just a few
things we'd like to ask
before you're destroyed.
Don't you know you
don't stand a chance?
Well, that's quite the plan.
We're in your backyard,
so we have the disadvantage.
In that case, I'll give
you a guarantee.
Listen, I don't come over to
the Heifong area very often.
[GENE]
Oh really?
So where's your usual
stomping grounds, then?
Ah, just around.
[growls] Jerk!
Now what are we gonna do?!
Accept the challenge,
whaddya think?
Gilliam! Launch the camera!
It'll be our scout!
[GILLIAM]
Be aware.
The conditions are even worse
inside the asteroid field.
Sending it too far would
appear to be useless.
Then you might say
that his traps wouldn't
stand chance in there either,
would they?
There's no sign of
the enemy ship at all!
Hey, Aisha, I want ya to
watch our back, ya got it?
Just leave it to me!
Dammit to hell!
Why did he pick a place
like this for a duel?
What kinda trick is
he tryin' to pull?
[MELFINA]
Missiles detected.
They're directly below us.
You're gonna pay!
Looks like he's got himself
some accurate missiles.
This guy's not foolin' around.
Now I get it.
So that's why he has
us stuck out here.
If we can make this a
close-quarters fight,
he's all ours!
[JIM]
There he is!
Ya sucker!
You won't get away!
Huh?
Where'd he go?
They're on our back!
What did you say?!
[growls] That asshole!
Tell me something, Gilliam,
is his ship more maneuverable
than the Outlaw Star is?
[GILLIAM] This ship utilizes
the most advanced
navigation system in the galaxy.
It's impossible that
my maneuverability
is inferior to a ship
of the same class.
Ya don't say...
Well this guy has no idea.
[MELFINA] Missiles closing in.
Ten o'clock high.
Just come at us from
head-on, damn it!
Yeah, the MacDougall
Brothers definitely have
some interesting tactics.
They sure like to sneak around.
[AISHA]
Wha--?
Starboard aft! Some more
missiles approaching!
[GILLIAM]
At four o'clock high.
No! Whaddya mean?!
He snuck up behind us already?!
There's no way we can shake
the ones on the right!
Then I'll swat 'em down!
I'm gonna have to go
all out against this guy.
[GILLIAM] Incoming missiles,
nine o'clock high.
[MELFINA] Missles coming in
from three o'clock high.
Count, five.
[ALL yelping]
Gene! If this keeps
up, we're history!
Don't worry. He'll be
out of missiles soon!
That's when the fight'll start!
Stop sitting around,
you birdbrains!
Blast your way in there
and smash him to a pulp!
You can't let him do
this to you anymore!
Shut up, Aisha!
If I could, I would!
[growls]
Don't tell me to shut up, you--!
[GENE]
I said to shut up, so shut up!
[AISHA]
You shut up!
[MELFINA]
Gilliam,
isn't it getting a little
too hot on the bridge?
[GILLIAM]
I'm sorry about that, Melfina.
I'll lower it two
degrees at once.
Ten o'clock high! More of 'em!
Agh! Got it!
[GENE]
Where's the El Dorado ?!
[GILLIAM]
I seem to have lost it.
Damn you, Gilliam,
what're you doin'?!
Why don't we launch the cameras
and position them all around us?
[GILLIAM] Our effective signal
range in these conditions
is about 100 kilometers.
It's unlikely that we will
receive any useful visuals.
Listen to me!
Plow through those guys!
Crush them into pieces!
And stop fooling around!
I told you to shut up, Aisha!
Right, like I'm gonna shut up!
Look, if you don't shut up,
I'm throwin' ya outside!
Why you--!
[growls]
Meow?
Throw her out... Wait...
Yeah, that's it.
Just like in the old days
when they had a lookout that
would give them a signal.
Like some kinda strong
light or something.
Aisha, I need you
to do me a favor
that can be done by
a strong Ctar-Ctarl.
Huh? What made you change?
I need ta throw you
off the ship, okay?
Meow?
Well, the odds aren't that
great really, but I think...
Well let's just say
it's a better plan
than keepin' this goin'.
Meow...?
By about now, they should
be sweatin' bullets.
You're probably right.
Huh?
Hey, Harry, are we
gonna fish 'em off?
Nah, I'm gonna play
with 'em a little more.
How many missiles are left?
We have 24% remaining.
[HARRY chuckles]
See. We have plenty left.
Let's sneak behind them.
[laughs]
Make sure that they don't
find out there's another ship.
Oh no.
There they are! There they are!
I found 'em!
Oh no, I think we've
been spotted!
Impossible!
Ship comin' in.
It's the Outlaw Star !
Yeah, now you guys are mine!
You think I'm goin'
down that easily?
I didn't know they had
the Grappler Arms!
You thought the El Dorado
was just an ordinary cruiser,
didn't ya?
[laughs] Gotcha!
Die! Die! Die! Die!
Die! You die!
Damn you!
Take over, Jim.
But why?
'Cause I'm going over
there and join 'em.
This is the El Dorado !
We've been caught by the enemy!
--This is the--
--[HARRY] Stop that.
If it's come to that,
don't worry. I'll settle it.
All by myself.
[TERRY]
Hey!
[TERRY groaning]
Oh, that hurt!
Ooh... You shot--
So, MacDougall--
Wait, you're not MacDougall.
Huh?
Now tell me,
where is MacDougall?!
So tell me, what
do you wanna know?
[GILLIAM]
Oh no. Warning, warning.
Uh? What is it, Gilliam?
[GILLIAM] Someone is
trying to hack into me.
And the source not available.
Engaging emergency protection.
Now I must say good night.
[JIM]
Gilliam.
[screams]
What is it?!
Stop it! Stay away!
So, you're MacDougall,
aren't you?
HHARRY]
Harry MacDougall.
Well that's the first time I've
given my name to an enemy.
I'm only gonna
ask you this once.
Why did the Kei Pirates
want the XGP ?
It was their ship in the
first place, isn't that right?
[GENE] Why did you wanna
have the XGP destroyed?
[HARRY] I don't ask my
employers for reasons.
[GENE]
Oh yeah? Who's your employer?
Well now-- Heh.
[HARRY]
I see.
So this is the
ship's main computer.
Hey!
[HARRY]
Oh, I've never met him before.
He just came to us with
a job offer, that's all.
[GENE]
Tell me about the XGP .
What's the whole
story behind it?
I really don't know
anything about it.
Hm... Well, the pirate
did say something
about being involved with
the Galactic Leyline.
What did he say about it?
[HARRY laughs]
[HARRY] I'm gonna trash
this thing in one minute.
Huh?
A woman?
[gasps]
No don't! Stay away!
[laughing]
I don't believe this!
Huh? What are you doing?!
You sick bastard!
[laughing]
Shit!
[screaming]
Ah! My arm.
I can't believe it!
You shot my arm!
Oh... Are you okay?
Yes, Jim.
[GILLIAM] The access seems
to have been cut off.
[GENE]
What does the XGP have to do
with the Galactic Leyline, huh?
I don't know... I don't know!
All right then, tell me this.
Why'd you destroy my
father's ship six years ago?
I don't know.
Six years ago, I was
only 12 years old.
Hey! You're a MacDougall.
And I keep on hearing about
the MacDougall Brothers.
Since you were just too
young to remember,
I don't mind asking your
brother, ya understand?
[HARRY]
Wait! Wait a minute!
Come to think of it...
where is your brother?
[JIM]
Gene! We've got a problem!
There's another one!
Another El Dorado !
How can that be?!
[JIM]
Get back here now!
Whaddya know... The brother.
Harry, what's the matter?
What happened?
Come on, answer me, Harry!
I'll blow' em to smithereens!
I'll blow 'em to smithereens!
[GILLIAM] Well, that
finally solves the mystery.
They didn't fly
circles around us
because they were
more maneuverable;
there was another ship.
This is no time for analysis!
Gene, I'm pullin'
out the assault bolt!
Turns out that other guy
is the real MacDougall.
What do you mean, "real"?
It's his older brother.
You're not getting away!
Ah, damn it!
[GILLIAM]
We're in danger.
Please take evasive measures.
Ah, shit!
You're hurting me, Ron! Stop!
Ow! My arm! My arm, my arm!
[RON]
Calm down, Harry. Calm down!
If you're a MacDougall man,
you don't get upset over
a stupid little scratch.
Right... I'm...
I'm so sorry, brother.
Hey... It's all right, Harry.
We're gonna do
a whole lot worse
to the man who's
done this to you.
[HARRY] You're right, and
I promise I won't back down
like that again.
[HARRY]
The woman...
That woman.
[JIM] It's hopeless. I'm not
picking them up anywhere.
[GILLIAM]
Enemy ship lost.
Okay, now what?
Like we have much choice.
We just go back to
Heifong and try again.
Sorry about that, Melfina.
It looks like I just
lost us another lead.
Huh?
Don't worry. It's okay.
[AISHA]
Hey!
Isn't about time you
guys picked me up?!
Boy, I never thought
I'd see the day
when I'd have to
apologize to Aisha.
We could always
leave her out there.
Nah, then she'd come back
and haunt me forever.
Okay, everybody, I'm tired of
this! You can come and get me!
[MELFINA]
Harry MacDougall...
What was he--?
I'm over here! Do you see me?!
I'm over here!
[GENE] It looks like we finally
get to take a break,
but then you gotta
work to live, right?
What's goin' on there?
Animal search and pest control?
Okay.
I'll leave the rest to you, Jim!
I'll continue to protect
the peace of the galaxy
if I have to, all for the
sake of one single girl.
Okay, I'm off on my date!
Next time on Outlaw Star :
"Advance Guard
from Another World"!
You better get ready!