[NARRATOR] Under the direct
command of Hazanko,
leader of the 108 Stars,
are the Anten Seven,
a feared group of assassins.
Tobigera, a master of disguise
and the tools of killing.
Hanmyo, a prodigy of space
combat, with the use of cats.
Iraga, a werewolf with
miraculous life force.
Jukai; his abilities
are shrouded in mystery.
Hitoriga, a man advanced
in the martial arts,
much like the leader
of the Anten Seven.
Hamushi,
a beauty who captivates men
purely by her sex appeal.
Shimi, a warrior whose skill
is such that there is no one
in the Pirate Guild who
has never heard of him.
If someone were
unfortunate enough
to make an enemy
of the Anten Seven
and forced to fight
against them,
I would say only this:
Farewell, friend.
[HITORIGA]
Lord Hazanko,
the Anten Seven are
now assembled.
[HAZANKO]
Hmm...
If you are the only ones who are
capable of taking this guy out,
he must be very good.
[JUKAI] Hazanko, would you
prefer that I deal with him?
I wouldn't mind at
all doing it myself.
Hitoriga, I've noticed the Anten
Seven seems to be short one.
[HITORIGA] Yes, Lord Hazanko
has anticipated this.
[HAZANKO] I have sent out
Shimi as the first assassin.
Well done, Lord Hazanko.
Without a doubt, knowing Shimi,
he will certainly carry
out your orders.
[JUKAI]
Wait!
This man may have
stolen the XGP ,
but he is still a mere
helpless Outlaw.
Why are we needed to kill
the likes of this man?
[HAZANKO]
Hmm... Gene Starwind is strong.
But his power should be
nothing to compare to yours.
However, I do sense a powerful
chi line flowing towards him.
As of now, it is
but a small sign.
Yet, if we leave it unchecked,
I believe he will come
to cast a dark shadow
upon the path we walk.
And so, I entrust you
with this very task.
In the name of the Anten,
you must seal
Gene Starwind's fate.
[JIM]
Gene, it's not lookin' good.
We're still way in the red.
We gotta earn
some big bucks.
Wake up, will ya?!
Are you listening?
[GENE]
Yeah.
[JIM]
Gene!
Aw, relax.
I already know. I don't need
you to keep on harpin' about it.
[AVATAR]
I love you! I want you!
[GIRL]
Liar!
[laughs]
It's so obvious.
You're taking it
all out on Jim
'cause you haven't
gotten a job offer.
That damn game of yours
is drivin' me crazy.
Will ya turn it off?!
[AISHA] Taking it out on me
won't do you any good either.
Why don't you just
talk to yourself?
Aw, shut up!
[laughing]
--[beep]
--Uh?
Ah! The game's over!
You made me lose! You idiot!
It's all your fault, Gene!
[GENE]
Aw, shut up.
I made some coffee.
[JIM]
Uh, Thanks!
[AISHA]
Aisha's really, really thirsty.
I'll have some, too!
What're we gonna do now?
You've always gotta have
some kinda plan in life.
If we could just solve the
mystery of the Galactic Leyline,
then we could all
have the treasure!
Yeah, I wonder what that
treasure is anyway.
[MELFINA]
Here you are.
[SHIMI]
Gene Starwind!
If you're in there, come out!
Huh?
[JIM]
Hm?
Wonder who that is.
Maybe somebody with a job offer.
Ah, great...
What do they want now?
[SHIMI]
Gene Starwind?
Yeah, that's right.
[SHIMI] Nothing personal,
but I'm here to kill you.
Oh, yeah? You a pirate?
[SHIMI]
And if I am?
I just like to know who
I'm doing business with.
What's your name?
[SHIMI]
I'm called Shimi.
I want to play a
little game with you.
Oh, a little game?
[SHIMI]
I challenge you to a duel.
I'll wait for you on Monkoku
Hill tomorrow at noon.
Bring any weapon you can carry.
If you refuse, I'll have
to kill your little friends.
[GENE]
Oh really? I don't think so.
[MELFINA gasps]
You waltz up here,
order me to come outside,
and then you challenge me?
Now I'm really pissed off.
Why don't we just
finish it right here?
You know, you're not
bad for a little guy.
[SHIMI] I always try to fight
fair no matter who I deal with.
That's interesting. You don't
look like the honest type to me.
[SHIMI] You've killed far too
many of us. Now I must end it.
I'll make a name for
myself by killing you.
That suits me just fine.
At least you'll be
known for somethin'.
[SHIMI]
You better believe it.
You just got lucky today.
But don't expect to
be lucky tomorrow.
I'm not like those
other careless punks.
Oh, is that right?
So who exactly are ya then?
[SHIMI]
I'd rather keep that to myself.
But if you beat me tomorrow,
then I'll tell you.
If I'm still alive.
So, Gene, are you gonna go?
[GENE]
Oh yeah.
[AVATAR] I love you!
I want you! I need you!
--[screams]
--[JIM] Gene?
[AVATAR]
I really want you!
[screams]
[JIM]
Gene!
Yeah, what do you want, Jim?
Don't you think you
should be getting ready?
[GENE]
For what?
That duel!
Just exactly how do you expect
me to get ready for a duel?
You know--
Hey, come on. Don't worry
yourself about it.
You know justice will
always provail.
Aw!
[grumbles]
[GENE]
Here, you try.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing
with this guy, Gene?
Yeah, sure. What's to know?
Right now, I'm goin'
out for a drink.
It'll be okay, Jim.
Gene's a tough guy.
[JIM]
Mh-hm.
But to be perfectly honest,
compared to a Ctarl,
he's not nearly as tough.
Hi, there. You having
a drink all by yourself?
How 'bout we go somewhere
else and have some fun?
No thanks, not tonight.
[WOMAN]
Oh, come on,
a cute guy like you
shouldn't look depressed.
[GENE]
This's the first time in my life
I've felt like drinkin' alone.
[WOMAN sighs]
[WOMAN]
You're no fun.
Hey, maybe next time.
[WOMAN]
Yeah, right.
That's a thought. I wonder if
there'll ever be a next time.
[MAN chuckling]
Hey, what the hell's
so funny, mister?
Forget it. I apologize.
Couldn't help but overhear
what you were saying there.
And lookin' at you
sittin' like that,
it sure does remind me of
myself when I was younger.
Aw, jeez...
Old people are always
sayin' things like that.
[MAN] Ah, hey, come on.
Just listen for a minute.
Whaddya say you and I have a
friendly little drink together
and we'll call ourselves
representatives of humanity?
Why not?
No matter what I do, seems
like every human on this planet
wants to drink with me tonight.
Maybe you should listen to what
your elders have to say, uh...
Um...
My name's Gene Starwind.
[MAN]
I know when you're young,
ya gotta be a smart-ass
even though you can't
necessarily do anything
to back it up.
[GENE] You sure got a harsh way
of lookin' at things, don't ya.
[MAN]
The name's Leilong.
Nice to meet ya.
[GILLIAM]
All systems of the Outlaw Star
are functioning normally.
Well I guess he really
didn't plan anything at all.
I'll tell ya, I don't
know about this.
Does that mean it's gonna
be a fair fight or what?
[GILLIAM]
Well, Jim,
perhaps they are afraid of
my foolproof guard system.
Must be nice. Machines
don't have any worries.
[GILLIAM]
Excuse me, Jim,
what did you mean by that?
Let me see. For you
to understand,
I'd have to do a major
up-grade on ya.
[GILLIAM]
So in other words,
you need money.
We need money to
service the ship.
Let's face it. We're
attacked by pirates.
Why does this keep
happening to us?!
[AISHA]
Melfina! What're you doing?
Get over here! I need your help!
[sighs]
[AISHA]
Mel!
[gaps] Coming!
This is a Ctarl-Catrl specialty.
Gejidabo stew!
Huh? Where's Gene?
Eat some of this and you'll
have the strength of five men!
[JIM]
Uh, wait a minute!
Is this safe for human beings to
actually eat and still survive?
Of course, you
pathetic human being!
Gejidabo stew has its
origins dating back
to year 1 of the Ctarl-Ctarl
calendar where--
[GENE] What I've been
trying to tell you
is that one of us is
gonna die tomorrow!
I suppose that you're right.
So listen, have you ever
been in a duel before?
Yeah, sure. I've had a few.
[chuckles] So you see,
ya lived through every
one of 'em, didn't ya?
I'm not making any excuses,
but let's just say at
the time I had no choice.
It was something I had to do.
In my own way, I show respect
for those who have died.
Respect. Respect.
[chuckles]
When you die, that's the
end of all it, right?
That's right. And living
means something to me.
That's why I'm still
alive to talk about it.
[GENE]
Hmm.
Well, I know one thing.
I sure as hell don't feel
like losing; not right now.
Of course, that's what
they've all said.
Oh well. I'd better
call it a day.
You goin' already?
[LEILONG] I have to watch how
much I drink of this stuff.
Take care of yourself.
[footsteps]
[MELFINA]
Are you okay, Gene?
What the hell is
your problem, huh?
Is that "nice girl" routine
just somebody's program, too?
What were you made for?
Why are you here?
I don't know! I don't know!
Don't you remember you said that
we would find that out, Gene?
[MELFINA crying]
Aw, shit.
[GENE]
What the hell am I living for?
[SHIMI] To live... is to push
all of you others aside.
[GENE]
That may be.
[gunshot]
[SHIMI]
Sorry, Gene Starwind.
I still want to
live. That's all.
[inaudbile]
Tht may be the last egg
I ever get a chance to eat.
Cut it out. There's nothing
funny about tha-- Ow!
Yeah, it'd be better for all
of us if you didn't lose.
But if you happen to lose,
don't worry, I'll look
after everything for ya!
Will you get to work and
make us some money?
Hah. Anyway, give
it your best shot!
Man, that lady's got no tact.
Good morning.
[JIM]
Morning!
Gene, let's beat this guy.
Even it means fighting dirty.
[GENE]
You got it.
Fun's just gettin' started.
Didn't think you'd
get here early.
[SHIMI] It's not polite to keep
your guest waiting, now is it?
[GENE] I'll leave as soon as
possible, if you don't mind.
[SHIMI]
From this life.
[GENE]
Let's do it.
[SHIMI]
Fine.
Wait.
I-If you don't mind, I really
don't wanna leave behind
a pathetic looking corpse.
[LEILONG]
Just as I expected.
Looks like I'm the only one
who can take you on now.
That you, Leilong?
You do have a real
name, don't ya?
Leilong is my real name.
My trade name is Shimi.
[GENE] So this guy was
your flunky, is that it?
[LEILONG grunts]
[LEILONG]
He was more like a pupil really.
He didn't have any
talent, so he died.
That's all it amounts to.
Oh yeah?!
What does this amount to?
Jim!
[JIM]
That guy's shield is powerful!
Use a Caster!
Shit. Use my trump card already?
[JIM]
Are you hurt?
[GENE]
The bullet just grazed me,
but the impact cracked a rib.
It's slowin' me down a little.
Okay, sucker!
Got 'im!
Is he dead?
A Caster, huh? You have
some very interesting toys.
Eat this!
I didn't think it could
take a direct hit,
not from a Caster without
getting little damaged.
[GENE]
What is this guy?!
Game over.
I suppose I could
just let you walk away.
You just don't get it, kid.
When you've convinced yourself
that you have the upper hand,
ya leave yourself open.
Never let your guard down
until the fight's over.
[LEILONG] This is the end
of the line, Gene Starwind.
Good-bye, Gene.
[JIM]
Wait!
Gene and I are a team!
You fightin' him without a
handicap isn't fair at all!
[MELFINA]
And I think so, too!
Melfina, not you!
Gene's important to me!
I will not let you hurt him.
You understand?
You will not kill him.
If you're going
to take his life,
you're gonna have
to kill me first.
[LEILONG] Melfina, I couldn't
possibly kill you.
Anyone else who stands in my
way, I will have to kill them.
[AISHA]
Hold it! Hold it right there!
I have to tell you
that if you kill him,
you'll be dealing with
Ctarl-Ctarl trouble.
[SUZUKA]
I'll act as his second, as well.
Gene's life is currently
in my keeping.
I would appreciate it if
you were not to take it.
Otherwise we can not be to sure
of the consequences, can we?
Well well. I see you
are good friends.
But you can't win;
you must realize that.
[AISHA]
I don't wanna hear that!
Aisha! Bastard!
[GENE]
Jim!
Run, you idiot!!
[JIM screams]
No!
[SUZUKA]
You'll pay for that.
Huh?
Suzuka.
I told you what would
happen, didn't I?
If I have to, I'll kill
anyone who tries to interfere.
You son of a--
Gene!
Well, it looks as
though you can't move.
That tends to makes the
challenge rather boring.
So then. What do ya
say to a one-shot fight?
[GENE] Sounds like
you're enjoying yourself.
[LEILONG]
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't.
But a job's a job.
Looks like we're ready.
Let us begin.
[MELFINA]
Gene!
Oh, Gene.
Where did he go?
[LEILONG chuckling]
[LEILONG]
So I'm finished, too.
I'm dying because
of a faulty gun.
Talk about bad luck.
You must try to survive them.
Must not let the
Anten Seven prevail.
What do you mean
the Anten Seven?
Now, there are six
of them after you...
[GENE]
A dud gun.
So my talent is just good luck.
And now everybody's dead.
That's too high
of a price to pay.
[JIM] You got that right,
Gene Starwind.
[BOTH gasp]
--Hey, Jim!
--[MELFINA] Jim!
Maybe this luck of yours
ain't so bad after all.
I agree.
It seems as though I need
to go back to training.
After eating that
Ctarl-Ctarl stew,
my whole system's been
thrown out of whack.
If I'm not mistaken, Suzu,
isn't that called
"shifting the blame"?
I would greatly appreciate it
if you didn't call me "Suzu."
[AISHA growls]
Gene! You better
not forget this!
That's another one you owe me!
Hurry up and solve the mystery
of the Galactic Leyline
and hand over the treasure
to me when you do!
Why do you suppose she keeps
saying things like that?
Maybe because the
lady's got no tact.
[JIM] He didn't kill us,
so maybe he was a good guy.
[GENE]
Good-bye, Leilong.
[HAZANKO]
Damn you, Shimi.
You were worthless.
[HITORIGA]
Please... leave it to us.
[HAZANKO]
Gene Starwind...
Now you have stirred
my curiosity.
I, Hazanko, want to meet you.
[LEILONG] Damn it. They sure
buried me deep enough.
Seeing all those people
made me start to get some
weird thoughts in my head.
[LEILONG] Maybe I'll have
to just treat myself
to becoming a
wandering Outlaw, too.
Good-bye, Gene.
[GENE] A dangerous job
will always come along
no matter what line
of work you're in.
Recovering a treasure
is one thing,
but you want me to
fight a space monster?
Here it comes! Here's the catch!
There's always a catch.
Huh? Fifty tons of Dragonite?
Five million wong?!
You got it! I'll do it!
Please, let me do it!
Danger is no problem!
Next time on Outlaw Star :
"Demons of the Water Planet"!
You better get ready!