[SAKISAKA]
What just happened?
[TABBY]
Weren't we here earlier?
[SAKISAKA]
Hmm...
Did we get transported?
[SAKISAKA] Is this some
sort of transporting device?
We should go right
back to those towers.
Let's go somewhere else.
I think if we keep looking,
there might be a chance
we'll find the same patterns
in the other Lost Grounds.
Did you forget that we're
looking for the Virus Cores?
I might be wrong, but I
don't think those patterns
have anything to do
with our search.
We don't know that.
What if they are
related somehow?
Come on. Let's go!
[SAKISAKA groans]
Yeah, okay, fine.
Haseo, we're going
to the next place.
Yeah. Alright.
[TABBY gasping in surprise]
Oh, wow!
Where... are we?
Is it your first time here?
Yeah.
Have you been
to this place before?
Yeah.
There used to be a
statue of a girl here,
but that was a
very long time ago.
[OVAN]
That's right, Haseo.
It's important to
recognize this game
has a very
mysterious autonomy.
Aura.
That was the name
they used to call her.
Neither the system administrator
nor any other entity
can control it.
In fact, parts of the world
are completely governed
by the rules of
the game itself.
Maybe she just lost
interest in the end,
lost hope for this world.
It does.
You must play this game with the
assumption that it does exist.
That is why we are known
as the Twilight Brigade.
Hey, Haseo, you in the bathroom?
[SAKISAKA]
Hurry up!
Coming!
[TABBY giggles]
Okay! Let's go!
Hey!
How are we supposed
to find these things?
I really don't think
it's gonna be very easy
to find an item that's
not listed in the specs.
[SAKISAKA]
I've never seen you like that.
What?
--It's not important.
Anyway, I don't think
there are any here.
[HASEO] Yeah, I doubt they'd put
the item in a place like this.
This is a pretty special
area, so I thought
maybe we'd find at least
one of the Virus Cores here.
Didn't Shino tell you?
The Lost Grounds
are unusual areas
that can't be touched
by anyone or anything.
I already know that.
[SAKISAKA] Not even the
administrator can modify
or delete it.
It appears and
disappears randomly.
Just like that last transport.
That would have been
impossible in the normal areas.
[HASEO]
I guess.
[SAKISAKA] But in the Lost
Ground, it becomes possible.
[TABBY screams]
--Huh?
[SAKISAKA]
Tabby!
Where'd she go?
Tabby, where are you?
Haseo, send her
an e-mail, right now!
Huh?
Hurry up!
I think I saw her
searching here.
[HASEO] I don't think
the e-mail went through.
[SAKISAKA screams]
Sakisaka...?
Where are you?
[ENDER]
Oh, my. Are you alone?
Aren't your friends with you?
Listen lady, That is
none of your business.
[ENDER]
C'mon kid, take it easy.
Don't hide things from me.
Now where did they go?
Three came in here,
but now there's only one.
What's going on?
If you don't answer me
now, you might end up dead.
[ringing noise]
[ENDER] Too bad,
something's come up.
See ya later.
[GORD]
Who has the Virus Core?
If you don't tell me,
I'll PK you.
Why are you after us?
Is it 'cause we're
members of Kestrel?
Yeah!
Why? You got a
problem with that?
It's only a rumor.
I don't know anything
about any Virus Cores.
I swear it!
I told you,
I don't know anything.
[GORD]
Oh man. You're useless.
Revive him and get out of here.
[BOY 1A]
Rip Maen.
Dude, I'm sorry!
I got stuck at work.
What's up with that craziness?
[GORD] Just my own little
way of collecting information.
[NASUBI] I can't believe
you're using violence
to get it out of them.
[GORD] Whatever.
Did you find any leads?
[NASUBI]
Well, something, but I...
[GORD]
What?
[NASUBI] I think
it's gonna be trouble.
[GORD] I've heard rumors that
it's someone from Kestrel.
Who is it?
[NASUBI]
Bordeaux.
You know who that is.
A player killer.
[NASUBI] It fell into her
hands purely by coincidence.
Very interesting.
Welcome back.
[HASEO]
Have you seen the others?
I heard about what happened.
Huh?
[SHINO] Sakisaka is
working by himself now.
But Sakisaka disappeared!
Yes, he did.
But, it's okay, I'll explain.
I'm pretty sure Tabby
will be back soon, as well.
Not here, huh?
[ENDER]
What are you doing?
[TAWARAYA]
Ender!
I just wanted
to ask you something.
Well, what is it?
Apparently, there's
more than one of these.
You know, it's not a
good idea to keep that here.
[TAWARAYA]
But I can't just let it go.
Either way,
they're gonna come for it.
So. What about you?
Have they made their move yet?
Taken the bait?
Disappeared.
Anyway, I think they'll
probably meet at Mac Anu,
so I'll just rest until then.
[TAWARAYA] What do
you mean "disappeared"?
The scars.
Haven't you heard about these
anomalies in the Lost Ground?
Oh! That's right.
I've heard those scars
can even distort the graphics.
I was thinking I should
name them pretty soon.
TaN is on the leading
edge of any trend.
We gotta live up
to our reputation.
So, what about them?
They seem to work
as a transporter.
So that's how you
lost the Twilight Brigade.
Where'd it happen?
Shut up, I didn't lose them.
[TAWARAYA]
Oh, it doesn't matter.
Where was it?
Hulle Granz Cathedral.
Oh!
That's the Lost Ground
that was just discovered.
[GORD] So I can find this
Bordeaux character there, huh?
Will you let me
ask you something?
Only if it's a question
I can answer.
Why on earth are you
spending so much time and energy
trying to get the Virus Cores?
And why do you
want to defeat Ovan?
How else am I gonna prove
that I'm better than he is?
What a childish motive!
...and before I knew it,
there was this flash
and I was inside of the wall.
There were all these weird
lines and stuff everywhere.
And I tried real hard to move,
but I couldn't, and I realized
I couldn't log off normally.
So I had to reboot
and log back on.
Where did Sakisaka go?
Don't worry.
Sakisaka is safe,
he's just working alone
for a little while.
Oh.
Sakisaka got hit by
a bug like you did.
But he came back right away.
He's off on a another task.
He was confused, but he's fine.
That's my teacher!
I was panicking and
struggling for quite a while.
I have to admit
I was a little confused,
and couldn't
recognize it was a bug.
Also, after hearing
what happened to Haseo,
I think it's too dangerous
for the three of you
to work together for now.
What do you mean?
After you and
Sakisaka disappeared,
that freak Ender showed up.
[SHINO] It's likely
you're being followed.
You must be very cautious.
Hmm.
[HASEO] So, what are
we supposed to do now?
[SHINO] Tabby, I want you
to continue searching
for the Virus Cores.
[TABBY]
Okay!
What about me?
I'd like you to check
out the information
you brought us about
the Key of the Twilight.
Information about...
... the Key?
The information you brought
to us regarding the items
that aren't listed in the
specs, and without them,
we'll be unable
to find the location
of the Key of the Twilight.
Don't you remember, Haseo?
Yeah, I do.
Good luck, you two!
Just hand it over,
and you'll spare yourselves
pain and embarrassment.
[BORDEAUX] Is this thing
really that important?
The item isn't even
worth anything to you.
[BORDEAUX laughing]
I guess sometimes it's okay...
...to become a
Player Killer Killer!
[SHINO]
You're still here.
[HASEO] Hey, the items
that aren't in the specs
are these Virus Cores, right?
[SHINO]
Probably.
Have a look.
Exactly how many of
these things are there?
If the rumors are true,
then there must be as many
as there are Lost Grounds...
So, six then.
But it's interesting...
These two are different colors.
Maybe the other ones
are also different?
You really don't think you
can take me down, do you?
I admire you for having the
courage to fight by yourself.
But it means nothing
if you're gonna end up dead!
Carelessness is
your worst enemy.
I'm a pro at fooling people.
[BORDEAUX]
Wait!
You can have it!
That's all you want right?
You're not putting
up much of a fight.
[BORDEAUX]
Always know your limits.
Damn you!
Now, are you gonna behave
yourself and give it to me?
[BORDEAUX]
Who are you?
Saving the weak!
Defeating the strong!
I am known as the PK of Justice!
But you can call me Gord.
All right. You win.
Here, take it!
Thanks for the gift.
More than anything else...
trust is the key
to good business.
I wonder how I
should hand it over.
What do you see?
[HASEO]
Hold on!
I think there's some
kind of significance
to the glowing lights
in these towers.
[SHINO]
What do you mean?
Maybe this is where
we're supposed to use
the Virus Cores.
[SHINO]
Haseo!
I'm pretty sure we
only need three more.
I bet we're gonna have to
find the colors that match
the rest of these towers.
[SHINO] Five Virus Cores
plus one for the final level.
There should be six in total--
as many as there
are Lost Grounds
that have been discovered.
[HASEO]
We have to tell Ovan!
[SHINO]
I'll tell him.
[SHINO] What will you do if you
find the Key of the Twilight?
[HASEO]
I don't know.
What about you?
[SHINO]
I think I'll...
...keep it a secret.
What do you mean?
Tell me, Shino,
what are you to Ovan?
No more than
an acquaintance...
...in the real world.
I'm going now.
I have to go let Ovan know.
Oh, I'll go with you.
Uh-uh. No, Haseo.
You keep looking
for the Virus Cores.
[HASEO groans softly]
I'm asking you.
Follow Ovan's wishes.
Thank you.
[OVAN]
Welcome back.
[SHINO]
Did you get my e-mail?
[OVAN]
Yes.
An amazing discovery, even
if it did happen by accident!
[SHINO]
Is work going okay?
[OVAN]
Yeah.
I really hope that we
can find it this time.
[OVAN]
As do I.
It's about time.
[SHINO]
Yes.
[OVAN]
If we...
[SHINO]
Huh?
[OVAN] If we find the
Key of the Twilight,
I think I'm going to
leave for a little while.
[SHINO]
Huh?
[OVAN]
If you can't reach me...
[SHINO]
What?
[OVAN]
Don't worry.
Did I just hear you say 'if"?
That's not like you at all.
And if I...
If I don't worry
about you, who will?
You'll push yourself too hard.
[OVAN]
The time has come.
[NAOBI] They've begun
working separately.
[ENDER] Do you want
me to follow them?
[NAOBI]
Just Haseo.
If he enters phase one,
you may commence.
I understand.
Tawaraya has one of the Cores.
What do you want me
to do about that?
[NAOBI]
Ovan is always thinking ahead.
Don't tell Tawaraya anything.
[ENDER]
Yes.
Every one of the Virus Cores
that have been found so far
were discovered in and around
the six Lost Grounds.
Here's another one.
It happened again.
What is this?
Where am I?
This is for Ovan's wishes.
It's him.
Well it looks as
though that damn Ovan
is about to make his move.
[ENDER] I've completed the
preparations as you requested.
[NAOBI]
Good work.
[ENDER] I'm hoping that
it will operate smoothly.
[NAOBI]
Are you uncertain?
[ENDER]
I'm not.
[NAOBI] What I want
is Ovan's character data.
As long as you can
transfer the data,
there's nothing
to worry about.
[ENDER]
Yes.
[NAOBI]
If you can trap Ovan,
everything after that
will follow as planned.
[ENDER]
Is that okay?
[NAOBI]
The guild has done a lot...
More than I expected.
I understand.
[OVAN] The path to the Key of
the Twilight has been opened.
[TABBY cheers]
Each one of the Virus
Cores is a different color,
and there are towers
with matching colors
in the Coite-Bodher area.
I think we can safely
assume that is where
the collected Virus Cores
are to be used.
I don't remember
anything like that.
Really? You can't recall
the five little towers?
Oh... I remember.
But don't you agree
it's probably kinda...
I mean, isn't it
a little too easy?
We couldn't be
that lucky, could we?
Yeah, Yeah.
[OVAN]
The Key of the Twilight.
It can turn the core program
of this game upside down,
shaking the foundations
of The World.
It exists within
the program...
Or it may live
within the program.
Is there more than one?
Or only one?
It would be enough
to answer this question alone.
[OVAN] This is our only chance
to get a head start on TaN.
[OVAN]
The time for action...
...has come.
Let's do it.
Now!