[TAWARAYA]
What's all this about?
[ENDER]
I wonder...
What do you mean,
"I wonder"?
We don't even know
the source of the story.
It's almost like
the speculations
are just
breeding more rumors.
Doesn't that happen
a lot on the forum anyway?
Sure... but...
In this case it's
a little different...
Ovan's involved.
You're right.
As TaN, we can't afford
to overlook this matter.
Oh no, we can't.
So the Black Adept Rogue, Haseo.
[OVAN] Don't worry.
The day will come
when you will.
Let's meet again soon, Haseo.
[SHINO]
I know it's hard...
But don't quit.
It's not stupid.
And it's not pointless.
Because...
we need you Haseo.
[HASEO] Ovan.
Are you Haseo?
And if I am?
About Haseo,
aren't you going to do
anything else
to convince him?
[TABBY]
Hey, Sakisaka!
Ovan... Are you okay?
I'm talking to you!
Ovan?
Hey! C'mon!
When the time comes,
everything will
fall into place.
Haseo...
We've only now
just planted the seed.
It's still too
early to harvest.
Haseo?
I beg of you! Please!
Accept our most profound
and humble supplication!
Ahh... Your what?
Aren't you the legendary
Black Adept Rogue,
Mr. Haseo?
Legendary?
[PC 3A]
You look like a Form 1,
but you have the specs
of at least a Form 3!
You're seriously cool!
Do you mind if we
team up with you?
[PC 3C] If we could
hang out with you,
we'd have nothing
to be afraid of.
Well?
Hey, wait!
[PC 3D]
I found you!
I never thought I'd meet
you in a place like this!
[PC 3E] The Enchanting
Black Adept Rogue, Haseo!
Now I'm "enchanting"?
Great.
[PC 3D]
He looks just like
any other Player Character.
[PC 3E]
Idiot!
That's because he's
a secret character.
[PC 3D]
I get it.
What?
[PC 3E]
Let's get to it!
[PC 3D] Please, after you!
[PC 3E] Oh man,
he's not giving up
any Chim Spheres or
rare items... loser.
[PC 3D]
That's right,
are you really the
Enchanting Black Adept Rogue?
I'm... Tanaka.
[PC 3E] Oh quit telling
such bold-faced lies!
[PC 3D]
Too bad.
Look, he doesn't
have much stuff.
[PC 3E] Whatever he has,
we're gonna take it!
You're Haseo, right?
Haven't you read the forum?
Um...
Everyone on there's
talking about you.
The Legendary
Black Adept Rogue.
The Enchanting
The modified rare character.
An A.I. character
whose player
doesn't exist
in the real world,
and has great range...
And you...!
What do you think I am?
I don't know...
Who, or what, you
might turn out to be
isn't important to me.
I'll tell you what
I'm really interested in...
Why, exactly has Ovan taken
such a strong interest in you.
Huh?
This whole ruckus on the forum
about you being special,
originated from Ovan himself...
That's my take.
Ovan? But why?
I mean, do you
actually know Ovan?
To give and take.
It's the principle
of business.
If you give me
all the information
that you have about Ovan,
Then I'll tell
you everything
that I know
about him... okay?
Well as far as
I know, Ovan is a--
Wow, hang on.
Ahh...
Just to let you know,
I don't wanna hear
about the strange man
looking for
the Key of the Twilight,
or the eccentric Master
of the Twilight Brigade,
that's all common knowledge.
What's wrong?
Go on, tell me.
But that's all I know.
What?!
Plants are very
mysterious things.
Even if you forget
that you planted the seed,
when the season arrives
it will naturally sprout.
And when its time
for them to die,
they leave new seeds.
The cycle can
then be perpetuated
by providing water,
light and nutrients.
What color flowers
do you like, Ovan?
Black.
Well, I'm pretty busy,
so I'm gonna be leaving now.
Hold on!
I told you.
Give and take.
That is the principle
of business.
Well...
First you need
to get stronger.
You were PKed
and you logged on again
because you don't wanna lose.
I respect that...
But you have to
get stronger...'kay?
What do...?
Why do you...?
How do you
know about me...?
Let's meet again!
How did it go?
Hard to say.
Uh-huh?
Y'know, I just
don't understand.
Why is Ovan so
interested in him?
Beats me.
Either way, Ovan's
interested in Haseo...
So it really doesn't
matter what we think of him.
Well, as long as Ovan holds
his interest in the newbie...
we as TaN have
got to make our move now.
Exactly.
Haseo!
Hey, Haseo!
You're that...
girl from...
The fresh new beginner
who just joined
the Twilight Brigade...
I'm Tabby!
Hey wait, Haseo! Haseo!
Hey, Haseo! Haseo!
Haseo!
What do you want?
Ovan wants
you to have this.
Ovan?
Uh... what is it?
What?
You don't know
what a guest key is?
How should I?
You joining
the Twilight Brigade?
You haven't
joined a guild right?
You know...
You should join our guild.
As long as you
have that guest key
you can enter
the Twilight Brigade's @HOME.
Ovan's waiting for you.
I know you're also waiting
to meet Ovan again.
Ovan.
Shino's waiting as well!
Oh come on!
Excuse me.
What?
Close your eyes
for just a minute.
Oh nice try.
I close my eyes
and you run away?
No...
I won't close my eyes!
I can't do it!
Um... Uh-what?
I thought I could keep
from shutting my eyes,
but I kept them
open in reality too.
Oh, they're
all watery now!
You're getting on my nerves.
Nya!
Ovan.
Have you made up
your mind yet?
Was that you?
Did you make that happen?
Huh?
What do you mean?
Just a second!
Don't play dumb!
What the heck was that?
What did you see?
Tell me what you saw.
I guess... it wasn't you.
Now I see.
I'm no longer surprised
why Ovan has his eye on you.
Because there is
something special about you.
The question is...
Who will you choose to give
that "something special" to?
[PC 3F ]
Hey, that guy...
[PC 3G]
Yeah, that's the guy
everybody's talking
about in the forum, Haseo.
[PC 3F]
No way!
And that's Tawaraya
from TaN with him!
Consider the
consequences of saying no
to the invitation
to our guild.
Think about it
very carefully.
I don't know.
[PC 3F] Wow, he's
already getting scouted.
[PC 3G] Yeah, of course
TaN's not gonna
ignore someone like that.
I don't know!
Oh I don't know!
He said I was getting on his
nerves and then he just left.
Am I annoying, Sakisaka?
Am I annoying?
I'm not annoying, am I?
Right?
[SAKISAKA] Well...
Well?
I'm perplexed
that I tolerate you,
and I'm surprised that
I still hang out with you.
Oh! There it is!
Your catchphrase!
Why, thank you!
So, answer my question!
Why, thank you.
I said answer my question!
Ovan, I think I need to
meet with Haseo one more time.
What for?
Well I...
It appears that TaN has already
started to make their move.
If Haseo decides...
Everything here
has been predetermined.
Haseo is...
Become stronger, huh?
Well ask me already.
Ask what?
Nevermind.
See ya.
Okay.
Not surprising.
So...
Waddya think
we should do now?
Who knows?
But, one thing
is absolutely certain.
There's definitely no doubt
that Haseo's existence
has become vitally
important to Ovan.
Haseo, welcome to the--
It's okay...
I can let myself in.
All I did was plant
the seed, nothing more.
About the rumors
that are accusing you
of posting those
messages on the forum.
What were you doing?
Ah, hmm...
Well I...