You can run away now!
Haseo.
Was that the player
who killed
over a hundred PKers
at one time?
You mean Haseo,
"The Terror of Death"?
The title's a bit much.
Anyway, we better
leave that psycho alone.
Master Yata!
It's Ovan... he's made a move.
So he's back.
Who is that?
Someone we're watching.
How long do you plan
to keep coming here?
Until you disclose
some insider info.
How's that?
I already told you,
I'm not an informant.
I was kidding.
I like hanging out
here just for the view.
Well I find it irritating.
Tell me Phyllo,
why do you think Haseo
stopped coming here?
I'm sure he has his reasons.
Yeah.
I really don't know.
They're calling him
'The Terror of Death.'
Well, I guess he can't
turn back anymore, can he?
Of course he can...
if he chooses to.
He's got another chance if
he's willing to take it.
And that's not
just in the game...
but in the real world too.
Willing to take it... huh?
I doubt he'll cool off.
What do you think?
It's all because...
Shino became a Lost One...
Tell me something.
Are you still planning on
supporting Haseo like this?
I'm sorry, I...
I don't want a Papa like that!
I don't think I can continue
to help him either.
But!
But I think supporting Haseo...
Enough. Let's go!
I guess Haseo must
be the way he is...
because Shino became a Lost One.
That's why.
Meow?!
Well, it's been awhile.
Saburo!
I thought you'd be at this
so-called "historical area,"
so I stopped by.
I see.
What's the
matter with you?
Well I...
There used to be
this dog that would
always be barking
on my way to school.
He was so annoying
but then he disappeared,
and instead of being relieved,
I really kinda missed.
You see as much
as it bothered me...
it was part of my day.
I guess...
it's kinda like that.
I'm not a dog... am I?
Well I guess you're a cat here.
You're so funny.
By the way, I heard
some rumors at Mac Anu.
But I'd take them all
with a grain of salt.
They're probably true--
all of them.
Maybe, but be reasonable.
What good is it if
you keep moping around?
I'm not moping.
It's just...
I know Haseo's actually
kind deep down inside.
That's why I can't decide
what to do about him.
Haseo is kind?
You're kidding, right?
Well...
You should know...
he often goes to
the Hulle Granz Cathedral.
I think he goes
there so he can pray.
Because it's a church?
It's not like that. I mean...
it's a special place for him.
You know, I should I should
be visiting it too.
So he goes there everyday?
I dunno.
But he ends up there every
time that he's logged in.
That's not like him.
He's thinking of
Shino all the time.
Don't you think that's kind?
He's such a sweetheart.
Shino?
Oh! Sorry.
You don't know her?
Haseo's like this...
because of Shino.
I really don't
know what happened,
But from what I can see,
he just wants to get stronger.
That's not true!
I know for sure that Haseo's
doing this to save Shino!
Okay, what about you?
Huh? M-Me?
Haseo's doing
something for Shino.
What are you doing then?
You're not doing anything, huh?
Wait!
Are you certain
you're okay with all this?
Have you ever considered
how Shino would react
to you being called
"The Terror of Death"?
Tri-Edge is not
the kind of opponent
you can defeat with
just your strength.
He's on an entirely
different level.
I can't stress enough
that this is not something
you can easily carry out.
No matter how
strong someone gets,
they're still no match
for Tri-Edge.
That's why Shino--
It doesn't matter
what Shino thinks!
Is that really what
you believe Haseo?
I'm gonna go help Shino now!
I'll deal with
your criticism later!
Stop and listen to me!
We should just
do things on our own.
We'd still have a good time.
Like I said, she wasn't that
type of girl to begin with.
Just get over it.
Come on, it
isn't even like that.
Look, I supported you when you
wanted to make a guild...
one that helps beginners
and intermediates
find their way around
this game, remember?
That is true...
Yeah. But not her.
All she ever wanted to do was
help The Terror of Death!
Well, I'm determined to do it.
I'm not gonna end things half
way like this!
I guess you're right.
I can't do this alone.
Look, we have to work together
if you wanna be serious!
What's going on?
It's an argument between
the Moon Tree Guild's
Sakaki and Haseo,
The Terror of Death.
Wow, that's like
mixing water and oil!
Moon Tree hates
Player Killers, right?
Yeah!
Let's go check it out!
As usual, I'm useless.
Phyllo!
Where'd you go?
Sorry, my cat and dog
were playing around
and pulled out the plug.
Never mind that Phyllo.
Haseo's over there!
You're saying you met him?
No, but...
I saw him fighting
someone in the plaza!
Almost time.
Ovan!
Hey!
Where do you think
you're going?
Oh Haseo...
Ovan!
It's been a long time, Haseo.
Or maybe I should call you
"The Terror of Death"?
You've gotten quite strong.
In fact much stronger
than before.
Well I was forced to
become stronger.
Thanks to you.
Haseo.
Always the reliable one.
I knew I could count on you.
When the Twilight
Brigade broke up,
why didn't you come back then?
Tell me.
What have you been doing
for the last six months?
Ovan, when you suddenly
disappeared, we all just...
How could you have
disappeared like that?
We were all waiting for you,
each one of us.
At the very least Shino and I
believed you were coming back.
The others began to doubt.
After that... Shino...
So I'm guessing
you want to know...
about Tri-Edge?
You saw Ovan?
That character...
it's really rare!
No one's seen him
for a long time.
Yeah, we saw him watching,
when Haseo was fighting.
Haseo was there?
He was, and as soon
as he spotted Ovan,
Haseo just took off after him.
Where'd he go?
I dunno...
But someone said they saw Ovan
at the Hulle Granz Cathedral.
When?
Just now, I think.
Apparently he was praying.
Look, He will be back today.
Can you guess where?
At the Hulle Granz Cathedral?!
Yes.
The place where
Shino was killed.
Tri-Edge is coming.
He's gonna be back.
Yes, finally...
I'll get my chance!
I swear I'm gonna be
able to bring Shino back!
Right Ovan?
Yes.
You and I.
We're the only ones who could
possibly bring her back.
We're the only ones.
Ovan?
I'll meet you
at the Holy Ground.
There are some
things I must do.
I have to know.
Is there anything I can do?
I wonder if he
really came here to pray?
Can I stay like this?
Just for a while?
Shino.
What is this?
What the...?
Master Yata!
There's an anomaly
occurring in the Cathedral!
You bastard! You're dead!
I failed...
I should've tried
to get his attention.
Well, if you're feeling regret
then maybe yes you
should have tried harder.
I wonder...
if Haseo has really become
The Terror of Death?
It doesn't matter.
You must now realize
that you're the only
one that can stop Haseo.
It's entirely up to you, Tabby.
Just me?
Really?
You can too, right?
Am I wrong?
My words don't get
through to him anymore.
It's the same with me.
He doesn't listen.
No, yours get through.
It's easy to tell that they do.
That's why he runs away
from you all of the time.
What is happening?
It seems that...
Haseo's battle with Tri-Edge...
has altered his data.
Has it been awakened?
No not yet.
What the...
Huh...?
It's been initialized?
Perhaps he's being data
drained...
What's happening?
This is--
You, shut up!
No.
I wasn't here.
Tell me...
What happened?
Haseo was...
It's true what they say about
getting really confused...
when so much seems to be
happening...
all at the same time.
Just stay calm.
What happened to Haseo?
He's been erased.
What?!