[TABBY]
Shino.
Do you have a minute?
Of course, but I
was under the impression
that you had quit the game.
After hearing about
what happened to Shino,
I realized I couldn't leave,
so I changed my mind.
Anyway,
that's the reason
why I'm still here.
Hey, so what did happen?
I don't know anything
aside from the
rumors I've heard.
[TABBY] Those rumors
have been bothering me.
That's why I'm asking you.
Um... Where's Haseo?
Did Haseo say anything?
[PHYLLO]
Why don't you ask him yourself?
He's not gonna talk about it.
At least not with me.
[TABBY]
I hope I didn't bother you.
Sorry.
[PHYLLO] You're the only one
that can be by his side now.
Go and talk to him.
That'll be best.
[inaudible]
Shino.
Why won't you log in?
Why won't you answer
your cell phone?
Ovan!
Why did you leave us
when we needed you most?!
Where are you?!
It's here--this one.
I've tried three times,
and it's the same sector
I can't crack open.
Master Yata?
Which data is it
that you can't seem to analyze?
If the information
is random to begin with,
there's no way we can
analyze it, anyway.
You're forgetting
our presupposition.
[PI]
If this is random null data,
then Ovan's escape
cannot be explained.
I understand that.
[YATA]
So?
Possibly, there is a
logic in the architecture
that might be unknown to us--
a sort of self-creating anomaly.
[YATA]
Sounds like science fiction.
But to be honest,
that kind of data
actually exists here now.
And also...
[YATA]
What?
If you're going to use
the term "science fiction",
remember that
online gaming itself
was considered
science fiction in the past.
You've got a point there.
[chuckles]
Well, in any case, we've
discovered an anomalous entity
that no one has come
across here in The World.
Furthermore, we've
confirmed the existence
of this entity
within Ovan's PC body.
[PI] Then we have to find out
what that entity is all about.
We'll also need to confirm
whether it has anything
to do with the Factor.
[YATA]
Pi?
[PI]
Yes?
[YATA] The outcome
will depend upon your actions.
[PI]
Yes.
Tell me, little one.
When was the last time
you saw Shino around here?
That's worrisome.
[TABBY]
There you are!
You were really hard to find.
I looked everywhere.
[TABBY]
Hey...
...what about that Sign?
I heard it appeared
when Shino got killed.
And what if it did?
[TABBY]
You were there... right?
I was.
And I couldn't
do anything--at all.
Not a thing.
[TABBY] Maybe if I'd
contacted you sooner,
it would have
turned out differently.
It wouldn't have
been any different.
[TABBY]
But--
--[phone ringing]
--Just a sec. Hang on.
--I gotta answer my cell phone.
--[phone ringing]
--[TABBY] Okay.
[HASEO]
Shino.
[TABBY gasps]
Haseo...
...what?
What happened to Shino?
Haseo!
What's wrong?
[TABBY] There's something
different about you, Phyllo.
[PHYLLO]
So did you see Haseo?
[TABBY]
That's why I came here.
But Phyllo, are you okay?
[PHYLLO]
Actually...
...I'm not doing very well.
[TABBY]
May I stay here?
[PHYLLO]
Certainly.
[TABBY]
Did something happen?
I'm thinking if that
really was Tri-Edge...
...we're in big trouble.
[TABBY gasps]
Did you meet him?
She's late.
[SABURO]
Oh, you are here.
Huh?
It is you, right?
Why'd you come from that way?
I got here early,
so I wandered over
to the Beast Temple.
It's like if you were
to visit Rockefeller Center,
it's not much different
to go further to Times Square.
Anyway, I think
your meeting place
is way too secretive
and a little too far.
You haven't changed.
Well, I guess my
PC body may be different,
but the inside's still the same.
Don't let it fool ya.
[PI] So since you
made it all the way here
using that character,
I can assume you're
accepting my offer?
Yeah! I like this PC.
I wouldn't be very comfortable
if I had to use
my previous character.
But you know--
[PI]
What?
I don't want to go back
into the secret service.
TaN doesn't exist anymore.
That means there's no longer
any secret service, either.
You shouldn't be concerned.
Then could you tell me why?
I'd really like to know
what you are trying
to get me to do
by giving me a
brand new PC body.
If it's the terms of use
you're concerned about,
don't worry, 'cause I'm
not gonna break them.
That sounds dangerous.
I get the feeling this character
has already broken
the rules, hasn't it?
So the question seems to be
whether or not you can deal
with that--nothing else.
Alright, I'll be in touch.
Oh, your name.
Are you gonna stick with Saburo?
That I can't give up.
Even though this game
is a different revision
with some changes,
The World remains the same.
I've given it some thought...
and I've decided.
[PI]
I don't really get it.
But if you don't mind,
then that's fine with me.
[PI]
What do you think you're doing?
Why'd we even bother
meeting in the dungeon
if we were going to
be seen together here?
Yeah, I guess...
But, I figured if it's
not the secret service,
then there's really no need
for us to sneak around.
[PI] You know what--
What is it you want?
About Tri-Edge...
So you have a connection.
[PI] Maybe I do,
and maybe I don't.
Lately, the rumors that
have been getting people
all hot and bothered
on the forum
have got me a little worried.
To be honest,
I don't even know right now.
Oh, yeah.
Another thing.
Isn't there gonna be
some kind of an event soon?
You mean the
time limited one?
Forest of Pain or something?
[SABURO]
Yeah, that's the one.
Are you guys involved in it?
I don't know who or what
you think that we may be.
But we certainly
do not have the power
to interfere in an event
controlled by the CC Corp.
I wonder.
A girl who dreams
of becoming a singer
could actually live
next to someone
who happens to be a
famous songwriter.
It's possible, you know.
[PI] I told you, I don't
get your metaphors.
Oh, well.
Your offer seems
pretty interesting,
so I'll use this character.
Thank you!
Keep in touch, okay?
[HASEO]
Where were you?
[PHYLLO] I'm not a
non-player character.
I have a real life, too.
It's not unusual for me
to leave sometimes--
you know--to feed my cats.
What happened to you?
It's not even bedtime yet.
[HASEO]
Um...
...nevermind. Next time.
Hey?
[PHYLLO]
Hm?
What do you
think about the rumor...
...on the forum?
There are a million rumors.
Which one exactly?
Haven't you seen it?
I don't know.
Which one?
The one that says PCs
who are killed by Tri-Edge
can't be revived.
The player in the
real world goes unconscious.
And then they become
a Lost One.
What about Shino?
I wasn't talking about Shino!
You understand?
We should go somewhere else.
Come with me, Haseo.
Why this place?
This is the spot where
I fought with Tri-Edge.
What?
Hold on.
You actually defeated Tri-Edge?
[PHYLLO]
No.
But wait...
I was under the impression
that if you met him,
you'd be killed.
[PHYLLO]
Yes, that's right.
I don't understand.
You're alive. How come?
[PHYLLO]
Haseo?
What?
The truth is,
for some reason,
Tri-Edge didn't find me
a worthy opponent.
[PHYLLO] I don't know why,
but he let me live
and simply disappeared.
Does that kind
of thing really happen?
Didn't I just explain
to you that it did?
Then why did he kill Shino?
Where is she now?
Shino is...
The real Shino is...
...unconscious.
She's in a hospital bed.
[HASEO] The way her
PC died wasn't normal.
I tried calling
her cell right away.
[HASEO]
Answer your phone! Come on!
Then I got a phone call.
It was from Shino's mother.
She saw your number
on Shino's call history
and called you back?
[HASEO]
She lives by herself.
Her friends started to
think something was wrong
and called her parents.
It turned out
to be pretty serious.
She...
[PHYLLO]
Huh?
[HASEO] She was alone until
the landlord opened the door,
found her on the ground
and called the ambulance.
All by herself.
If her friends hadn't called--
[PHYLLO]
What did her mother say?
[HASEO]
She said that if I...
...if I knew to call,
I must know something
about why this happened.
Like I was responsible.
[PHYLLO] It must have
been terrible for you.
[HASEO]
But it is my fault.
[PHYLLO]
Haseo.
[HASEO] I told you,
it is my fault!
Because...
...if I just got to the
Cathedral sooner--
[PHYLLO] It wouldn't
have made a difference.
Even worse, you could've
ended up as another victim.
But I w--
If that really was Tri-Edge,
you're definitely
no match for him.
[HASEO] So is this field
special or something?
[PHYLLO] It looks like
a normal field, but...
I can kinda understand
the Lost Grounds,
but right here?
Why would he...
...Tri-Edge...
Why would he come
to an area like this one?
Why were you here, Phyllo?
[PHYLLO]
Huh?
How come?
I was here by chance.
You're always holding
court in the same place
in the Mac Anu canal area,
and you're telling me
that you came here by chance?
Am I really supposed
to believe that, Phyllo?
Spit it out!
Shino and Ovan...
This is where they
first met each other.
You have to be stronger.