[SAKISAKA]
Hold on a second.
--Huh?
What the heck
are we doing here?
We haven't even found
all the Virus Cores yet.
[OVAN] The remaining
two will move our way
because we are here.
Yeah, I suppose...
But we'll be screwed
if TaN surrounds us
in a place like this.
What are we gonna do then?
We'll be fine as long
as we stick together.
Have faith.
Aren't you coming, Teacher?
I... know what's gonna happen.
Huh?
[TABBY]
Hey, wait!
[BSET]
I won't let you go!
[GORD] It has nothing
to do with you!
[BSET]
Of course it does!
[GORD] Why? You quit
when I did, remember?
[BSET]
That's not it.
[GORD] You know what
my objective is, right?
This is my only chance.
If I want to defeat him,
I have to act now.
The information is
leading me this way.
I understand that.
I don't think you do!
He wasted our time on
something that doesn't exist!
You remember, don't you, Bset?
You quit as well.
[BSET]
Yeah.
All that aimless searching.
It must have been
especially upsetting for you.
Yeah, but...
...no one forced me.
I followed him out
of my own free will.
How very gracious of you.
But me,
I won't ever forgive him.
I think you're wrong, Gord.
What are you talking about?
You know what?
I really don't care
if I'm wrong.
He's gonna pay for all
the times he tricked us
into working like dogs.
Ovan's gonna regret
ever meeting me.
And this will be
the end of him.
[NAOBI]
Is everything ready?
[ENDER]
Nothing's been overlooked.
[NAOBI] Ender, you know
what your job is, I assume?
I chase him into
the highest floor.
He finds himself trapped.
Then he's ours.
[NAOBI]
Exactly.
I won't tolerate failure.
There's evidence
of someone
secretly investigating
our illegal activities.
Who could it be?
The Administrator?
[NAOBI]
No.
Who else, then?
[NAOBI] Don't let it
be a concern to us.
It's about time for us
to leave this place, anyway.
And also...
Ovan isn't the type to be
lured out like this very often.
We only have this one chance.
I understand completely.
Hey, Ovan?
Uh, Ovan, I'm
going to go, uh...
...get the other Virus Core.
--Huh?
Are you?
How do you know the whereabouts
of another Virus Core?
[SAKISAKA]
Well, I, uh...
I'm certain that Tawaraya
from TaN has one.
Tawaraya has one?
You guys know each other?
[OVAN] The most important
thing right now
is that we get
the Virus Cores.
[SAKISAKA]
Well, I'll go get it then.
But Ovan...
Do you want me
to come with you?
Do you think you
have the courage?
It seems kinda scary,
but if I'm with
Teacher, I'll be fine!
[SAKISAKA]
Don't bother.
The game should be
enjoyed, right?
Huh?
That leaves one more.
Our friend Gord.
He'll be here soon.
[PC 9A] He's not
here today, either?
[PC 9B] Is he really
gonna trap the Brigade?
[PC 9A]
As if.
[PC 9B]
Yeah, really.
I wonder what
they're up to.
What the...?
Start by eliminating
the weakest.
After that,
wait for my command.
[ENDER] The tastiest part
should always be left for last.
We're not running, are we?
I can take 'em!
For the sake of our goal,
I don't intend to leave now.
Huh?
Ovan, you're sure?
I'm goin' for it!
Just keep them at bay.
Hopefully we won't have
to fight them long.
We just need time to get
the other Virus Cores.
Battling monsters
is acceptable,
but it is not the way
to gain true strength.
The only way
to gain true strength
is by fighting unpredictable
player characters.
Isn't that right?
Become stronger, Haseo.
The time is now.
What about you?
You don't need
to worry, Tabby.
I'll be all right.
[TABBY]
But you're a Harvest Cleric.
It's okay, I'm still
able to fight.
[HASEO]
Here they come!
[BSET]
I wonder...
...what's happening with them.
Are you really
that concerned?
[BSET] And don't say it
doesn't have anything
to do with me.
I still haven't come
to terms with everything.
[PHYLLO]
I see.
Ovan's dream
is to get a hold of
the Key of the Twilight.
Sometimes I wonder if he will.
Ovan isn't the type of man
you need to
worry about, is he?
[BSET]
I guess not.
[PC 9C] I heard the Brigade
finally made a move.
Wanna go watch?
[PC 9D]
No way!
A group of Player Killers
just headed that way.
I don't wanna get
caught up in that.
It sounds like the competition
for the Key of the Twilight
seems to be finally underway.
Well...
[PHYLLO] If you're that
concerned, you should go.
I can't...
Sometimes it's better to forget
about what's holding you back...
...and let your
actions speak for you.
Go on! Get moving
before it's too late.
If you don't, you'll
undoubtedly regret it.
You're gonna have
to give that up!
It was mine in
the first place.
Why don't you go get your own?
But it's completely
useless to you.
Even so, it's still
valuable merchandise.
Hey, Tawaraya,
wanna know why I came
here all by myself?
To steal the Core
back from you!
I'm not leaving
here empty handed!
Whoa, whoa, you're a
little worked up!
I was planning on
giving it to you,
but I don't feel
like it anymore.
I'll take you on!
You have no idea
what it means
to do things for the sake
of your friends, do you?
The sake of your friends?
That's certainly rich.
I guess it's okay to fight
with another PC once in a while.
[TAWARAYA vocalizes]
Don't be fooled...
...I'm very strong!
Gord! What are you...
Why are you here?
Look, we have backup!
Someone's come to help us
fight all these goons!
It's Gord!
I don't get it.
Why'd you show up to help us?
I'm trying to fulfill
my goal to defeat Ovan!
Tabby, keep your
focus over here!
Why'd you decide
to strike now?
Because the information
is on my side.
[HASEO]
Information?
From Tawaraya?
[GORD]
Who is Tawaraya?
You guys need another one
of these things, am I wrong?
Where did you find that Core?
Ovan's been looking
for it this whole time!
I know he has...
I've been aware of that fact
much longer than you.
Tell me, why?
The reason's simple.
Picture this:
the Key of the Twilight
is right in front of him,
but he's unable to possess it.
Wouldn't you like to see Ovan
in a situation like that?
[HASEO]
No, I wouldn't!
I see.
Well, then...
Time to die!
Well, Ovan, your friends
are all on the verge
of getting killed.
Are you just gonna stand
there and let them die?
You've got it wrong.
My people aren't the types
to give up that easily!
More to the point...
You should be less
concerned about their demise
and more about your own.
You shouldn't have said that.
You got me...
and now you're
gonna pay for it.
[SHINO]
Tabby, how're you holding up?
Huh?
If Haseo can get
through to Gord...
I'm sure he'll understand
and come to help us.
But until then...
We have to keep fighting.
We need to keep
TaN's troops occupied.
And we can't allow
them to defeat us.
Shino, I have a question.
If the Key of the Twilight
doesn't exist...
you'd tell me, right?
If it didn't...
I wouldn't know what to do.
That's right!
Okay Shino, this time
I'm gonna protect you!
[TAWARAYA]
Have you had enough yet?
[SAKISAKA coughs]
I... just can't.
I can't disappoint them
and come back empty-handed.
I'd really like to get this over
with as quickly as possible.
[TAWARAYA]
That's a wrap.
Man, you really don't
know when to quit, do you?
Bset, you're here!
It took a while
to find this place.
I hope I'm not too late.
I appreciate it.
It's good to see you, Shino...
But maybe you should thank me
after you find the
Key of the Twilight.
You bet I will.
[TAWARAYA] You're out
of items, aren't you?
Give up.
I'm not gonna give up.
I can't go back there
and face them...
...empty-handed.
Are your friends really
that important to you?
It's only a game.
Don't get so excited.
I don't think it matters
how you meet someone.
A friend is always a friend.
[TAWARAYA scoffs]
Even though I can't
see their real faces...
Even when they weren't...
...when they weren't
telling the truth.
I... honestly believed
them, you know.
[TAWARAYA]
You believed them, huh?
Take this!
It's all yours!
I can't stand it when
people get melodramatic.
Hey! Wait!
Human beings are such
strange creatures.
Time and again they'll choose
loyalty over common sense.
Oh yes, that's right.
Just a little bit more.
Is that Bset?
Why...
Why aren't they running?
Everything's going
exactly as I planned.
Good boy, Ovan.
The Key of the Twilight.
Ovan wasn't
deceiving you, Gord.
I know for certain
it really does exist.
What are you two guys gazing
into each other's eyes for?
Hey, Sakisaka!
So, you gonna tell us
what happened?
Look what I got!
That's awesome!
It's my teacher!
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcone to phase two.
[TABBY]
It looks like they gave up.
[SHINO]
I don't know about that.
Welcome back.
I'm not here to
join your guild again.
I got a Virus Core!
Check it out!
Yay, Teacher!
Ahh.
Congratulations on
a job well done.
Good work.
Thanks.
Look, everyone's
here now, Ovan.
Yes, they are.
Haseo.
The item.
Here it is.
So this is it.
Follow them!
Ovan, we're gonna
let you go on ahead.
[OVAN]
I'll leave it to you.
You better stay where you are.
We're not letting you stop Ovan.
No matter what.