[HASEO] Looks like we
haven't sparked any rumors
even though we've disbanded.
[SHINO] It's probably
because people realized
it has nothing
to do with them,
and they've grown tired
of talking about us.
[HASEO]
I guess so.
And what about Ovan?
Have you heard
anything from him?
His cell phone isn't
even working anymore.
I see.
Can I...
...ask you something?
What is it?
[HASEO]
Your... Your cell phone number.
I'm afraid you
might disappear, too.
Don't worry, I won't leave!
Maybe I am worrying too much.
Got something to write on?
[HASEO]
Uh... uh, yeah.
[SHINO] Here,
I'll give you my number.
If something happens--
No, even if nothing
happens, you can call me.
[HASEO]
Okay.
I'll give you mine, too.
Wanna do something?
Practice Rengeki--
Not that again.
Yeah, you're right.
You know what?
It doesn't feel like
the Brigade's disbanded.
Huh?
I feel like we
could go to our @HOME
and Shino would
be there just like before.
Hey, listen...
What is it?
The Brigade's gone,
and so is our headquarters.
We don't have
an @HOME anymore.
I guess so.
She's probably hangin' around
in a field or in town...
waiting somewhere
for Ovan to show up.
Y'know, when the
Twilight Brigade was together...
Every single day
was so much fun.
I have an idea!
Teacher, why don't
we just make our own?
Own what?
Our own guild!
Seriously?
Come on! Let's go!
Let's go apply
for our own guild.
Wha...
Well then...
What do you think
we should call it?
I see you're alone again today.
Shino was with me
just a minute ago,
but she had to log out
'cause she's got
a paper to do for school.
Duty calls.
Don't you have one of
those to do yourself?
Whaddaya mean?
A term paper.
Yeah, but I don't
feel like doing it.
It has nothing
to do with how you feel.
Sometimes you have to do
what you have to do.
I just won't feel comfortable
until Ovan gets back.
Just because Shino logged out
doesn't mean I feel
okay doing the same.
I don't know.
What exactly was that thing
we were searching for, anyway?
[PHYLLO] You've asked
that same question before.
Yeah, I remember.
[PHYLLO]
I suppose it turns out
that the Key of the Twilight
isn't real after all.
--[HASEO] But...
--Huh?
Do you really think Ovan
would've wasted
his time like that?
I don't understand
what you mean.
Well, I have no doubt
he totally believed it existed.
Are you surprised
such an eccentric man
believed in something
that isn't real?
It's just not like Ovan.
Don't you think?
I suppose that could be true.
[PI] We still cannot
trace Ovan's whereabouts.
[YATA]
The search must continue.
At the same time,
analysis of the data
we have so far
must be done quickly.
I understand completely.
Boy, Teacher sure is
taking a long time.
[PC 13A]
Hey!
[SAKISAKA]
How's it goin'?
[PC 13A] You're still
hangin' around here?
Everyone's already
switched, you know.
You should come
with the rest of us.
[SAKISAKA]
Yeah, so I've heard.
[PC 13A]
As long as you know.
Well I'm gonna get my stuff
ready and cancel my account.
[SAKISAKA]
Okay.
[PC 13A] I'll be waiting
for you over there.
Oh, just hang on a second!
[HASEO]
You like those?
[SHINO]
Mmm-hmm.
You had one...
...at the Twilight
Brigade's headquarters.
I don't have much room
for plants in my apartment,
so I thought I'd at least
like to have one in the game.
I asked Ovan if it was okay.
He said he liked them, too.
[HASEO]
I see.
My place is cramped.
I live by myself.
[HASEO]
Hmm?
I have so many bookshelves,
but not enough space
for other things.
Dracaena Massangeana.
The Tree of Happiness.
When I live in a bigger house,
that's the first thing
I'm going to buy.
Well, when that happens,
I'll buy you one as a present.
Sometimes you say
the same things as Ovan.
The same as Ovan... right.
[SHINO]
Let's go.
You're late and you're
also in a bad mood.
Did something happen?
I'm bored.
We made a guild and
there's still nothing to do.
[SAKISAKA]
Right.
[TABBY]
Oh! You wanna do something?
[SAKISAKA]
I think I'm gonna quit.
You're quitting?
Why all of a sudden?
I'm still sore about
what happened with the Brigade.
I-- This game isn't fun anymore.
You can't quit.
My friends in the real world,
they've invited me.
[SAKISAKA] Have you heard
of the game Riot Gun?
No.
That's, uh...
what I'll be playing.
You're gonna quit even
though we made a guild?
I'm sorry, Tabby.
I honestly thought
I could forget about
the Twilight Brigade.
But I don't think I can.
Don't go.
I know, why don't
you come with me?
I dunno...
Shino's still playing, so...
But of course.
[SAKISAKA]
Well... take care!
Do you remember this place?
You and I have been here before.
Yeah. I recognize it.
And remember,
you asked about Ovan,
and I told you that over
time we had become alike?
--Huh?
--When you wanted to know
what I was to Ovan.
When you said that
you'd become like him?
I was telling a lie.
[HASEO]
A lie?
The truth really is...
I admire him deeply.
Don't you think it's wonderful
that he's been able
to make a home for all of us?
You wanna know what?
I think I wanted to become
someone like that...
to make people feel at home.
But Shino, you are.
Even though I
disbanded the Brigade?
You gave me something--
A reason to stay.
What the heck just happened?
Is this what I think...?
[HASEO]
You know what this is?
Nothing to worry about.
[TABBY giggling]
Even in the game,
I'm all alone.
[PHYLLO] Worrying so
much won't do you any good.
[SHINO] Using clichés like that
won't do you any good, either.
[PHYLLO]
You're right.
[SHINO]
You're the one who always
picks on my choice of words.
[PHYLLO] So, you still
haven't heard from him?
[SHINO]
I think I will soon.
[PHYLLO]
Why is that?
[SHINO]
I just have a feeling.
[PHYLLO] It would be nice
if he'd come back.
If something should
ever happen to me,
please take care of Haseo.
Look out for him.
What are you trying
to tell me, Shino?
If you were to disappear,
he'd go nuts.
I can't even imagine.
He might even go
and kill himself.
Are you kidding?
I'm not entirely joking.
But there is some truth to that.
Don't you agree?
He's been really
helpful in so many ways.
I'm glad that Ovan asked him
to join the Twilight Brigade.
Seriously.
That's why I want you
to take care of him
if something
should happen to me.
Promise me that.
This isn't like you at all.
Maybe you're right.
[TABBY]
Wait a minute!
It's been a while.
Yeah.
What do you want?
Do you have a second to talk?
Well, there's
nothing you can do.
You can't stop someone,
especially if they
really wanna leave.
I know that, but...
So, what are you going
to do without Sakisaka?
I'll probably stick around,
for a little while,
just hanging out.
Stick around
for a little while?
What do you mean?
I'll see how it goes,
then I'll probably quit.
I'm not gonna stop you.
Well, I didn't ask you to...
I don't expect you to begin
to understand what I'm feeling.
What if Shino were
to try to stop you?
Would you stay then?
Probably.
But...
...Shino hasn't been in
touch with me at all.
Well, she's logged in right now.
You know what, Haseo?
You don't have to rub it in!
Man, what was that for?
Well, I'm going now.
Where to?
Where I'm going
is none of your business.
Sissy.
Yes!
I'm gonna get even stronger!
[HASEO]
Those guys!
[TABBY]
Well, you're pretty awesome,
but you can't really
replace Ovan, can you?
Oh! Looks like company!
And he's all by himself.
I know you.
Didn't we PK you?
[ASTA]
When was that?
[IYOTEN]
Pathetic!
[ASTA] All these newbies joining
the game are so easy to kill.
It's just no fun.
Oh. That's Ovan's groupie.
That guy's a serious weakling!
He is.
A pathetic weakling
like that just doesn't belong
in this world.
Let's take him out!
[BOY 1B/PC 8B] Let's make
him die--painfully.
Bring it on!
It'll be my pleasure!
[SHINO]
So Sakisaka left the game?
[TABBY]
Yeah.
I see.
You know what?
Oh! What...?
Shino!
Shino, are you okay?
Answer me, please.
I'm sorry. It was
nothing--A message.
I've got to go to Hulle Granz.
Right now?
Tabby, I'm sorry.
We'll talk a little later, okay?
Shino, what's wrong?
[HASEO]
What was that?
[IYOTEN]
Another bug?
The two of us will
be enough to kick his butt.
[ASTA screaming]
You're dead!
What the...
I didn't realize
how strong you actually are.
[TABBY]
Haseo!
What are you
doing right now?
Shino went to the Hulle Granz
Cathedral in a hurry.
Have you heard anything?
The Cathedral?
That's weird.
Why would Shino
need to rush over there?
I'm not like her.
Aura lost hope for this world
and decided that
she had to run away.
[TABBY] Hey, Haseo,
are you listening to me?
No, I'm not listening.
I'm on my way.
Haseo.
[SHINO]
[HASEO]
Shino!
Shino, hang in there!
Repth.
Repth!
Talk to me...
Hey! Shino!
[phone ringing]
[HASEO] Come on Shino,
answer your phone!
Come on!
Please...
Please! Hurry!
Shino!
Shi...
Shino.
Shino!
[TABBY]
You guys seem to be close,
so I thought you could
pass on a message to Haseo.
[PHYLLO] If you like, but why
don't you e-mail him yourself?
[TABBY] I can't tell
my rival that I'm quitting
because Shino is gone.
[PHYLLO]
Rival?
When I told Haseo
that Shino was in trouble
in the Cathedral,
he went.
He chased after her right away.
I... I tried,
but I just
couldn't go after her.
I understand.
[TABBY] So, will you
please let him know?