[OVAN] So this
is the last one.
[SHINO] It's okay,
you're safe now.
[TABBY] Why did
that Player Killer
do such a horrible thing?
I know...
[SAKISAKA] Hey, what
did this guy look like?
I'm not sure...
Did you see him?
I don't remember
it that well...
But, it wasn't a guy...
...it was a woman.
She was really strong
and I had no chance.
I just heard a rumor
that Gord got PKed.
It couldn't be
the same person, could it?
What are you
thinking, Sakisaka?
I don't think
Tabby was randomly PKed
and I suspect that our
Brigade is being targeted.
But, Gord isn't a
member anymore.
And besides, why would
anybody target the Brigade?
That's what
I'd like to know.
Did she say anything?
She asked me
about our guild.
And?
I told her I just joined
and didn't know anything.
[HASEO] Stop mumbling
just 'cause you got PKed.
Well, what
about you, huh?
Excuse me?
Arguing is forbidden here.
But Shino, since
this guy joined...
Nothing must be
done out of revenge.
But...
This is a time
for patience.
It makes me angry.
But I don't like
PKing or getting PKed,
so I agree with Shino!
It's just a game,
so it's gotta be fun!
Well, what can I do?
[BSET] I wonder what
the Twilight Brigade
is doing right now.
[PHYLLO] If you really care
you should join them again.
My interest doesn't
go as far as caring.
When she came after me
I told her
I didn't know anything.
I hate to admit it,
but I sincerely
don't know anything.
It really has
nothing to do with us.
As long as
you're not planning
to have anything to
do with the Brigade.
It's not that easy
to try and make
a clean break.
It's about the job you
gave me the other day.
[TAWARAYA] You need
to be more specific.
Umm, you wanted me
to check out a
certain Player Character.
Is there a problem?
You getting complaints?
No, but in addition
to compensation I
was given something strange,
and I'm not sure
what to do with it.
There's nothing wrong
with accepting a tip.
But, it's an item
I've never seen before.
Where's the guy
who gave you that?
He took off.
Find out where he is
and contact him immediately.
I'll take care of this.
Okay.
Haseo, wait a second!
It's too dangerous
to be out alone!
Listen, Tabby,
I'm not like you.
Anyway, stop
following me, will ya?
It's strange for this
to be happening now.
Yes.
Why has a new Lost Ground
suddenly appeared?
And why is it here?
There was a dragon sleeping
at the bottom of this lake.
I heard that to gain
strength it was eating
any monsters and travelers
who looked into the water.
And one day,
it revealed itself.
Yes.
That's the kind
of place this is.
It would be nice if things
would go smoothly from now on.
They will.
They're not
the types to withdraw
just because
someone was PKed.
I know.
Why don't you
talk to them?
Because that's your job.
I'll leave it to you.
I see...
Do you know what that is?
[NAOBI] Yes.
It's an anachronism.
An anachronism?
There were lots of them
in the old game.
Where did you get it?
I can't say.
It seems your anachronism
was being passed
around by many players.
Interesting.
Nobody knew
what to do with it.
If you want to disturb
the Brigade, use this.
And depending
on how you use it,
some interesting
things could happen.
Is that so?
[ENDER] Hold on a sec!
If it's work involving
the Brigade I'll do it.
Concerning the use
of this item,
it's better if you
leave it to Tawaraya.
Well, then. I'll be going.
You're always here.
I had a feeling you'd come.
I wanna talk to Gord.
Where is he?
Is this your friend?
My name is Tabby and I'm a
member of the Twilight Brigade.
Pleased to meet ya.
You can call me
Phyllo, young lady.
You've been through
a lot, haven't you?
Tell me where Gord is.
My guess is he's probably
somewhere in this town.
Did you see him?
No, he's with Bset.
I heard that someone
was chasing her as well.
Really, Bset?
Yes, I think she and Gord
are still in the alchemy area.
You'll always find
Bset there, guaranteed.
You've been there,
haven't you?
So, I'm your second
choice after Haseo?
We have different
plans for you.
In business, you have to look
into any opportunity
that could be profitable.
Profitable?
We've decided that
you might be useful.
That doesn't sound
like a compliment.
Here, think fast!
Ovan has his eye on that.
He wants this?
To be honest, I have
no idea what it is...
...or what he's planning
to do with it.
However...
So what's the big deal?
This item is not
in the game specs.
Not in the specs?
Key of the Twilight?
You never know,
it could possibly have
something to do with that.
So ask Ovan about it.
He is your guild master, right?
You really
don't know anything?
Now, that's a problem.
You see,
if he doesn't
pass along information
to his members,
it means he doesn't
trust you guys.
Or possibly,
he's just using the guild
and is going to take
whatever you find for himself.
Impossible.
Quit then...
...to come work with me.
I think I'll
hang on to this.
Thanks, come again.
Hey.
Where's Gord?
He's not around right now.
Logged out?
No.
But you should leave him
alone for a little while.
Gord has been flaunting around
his plans to defeat Ovan.
You know that,
don't you?
He was just PKed
by some unknown player
and I'm guessing he's
still a little bit freaked out.
He wants to defeat Ovan?
Do you feel that way too?
Of course I don't.
Are you a newbie?
My name's Tabby!
Who are you?
Are you targeting Ovan too?
No. I'm not.
So, what is this about?
Did you get PKed?
No.
Because I was in town,
I was only chased.
Well, do you happen
to know who it was?
What're you gonna do?
At your current level
you'll be quickly defeated.
But I...
Ender.
Ender?
You know her?
[HASEO] Well no,
but why is TaN...
TaN?
Wait! Haseo!
You know Ender,
don't you?
You do, right?
I don't know her!
But, just a minute ago...
Hey, just stop following me.
It's too dangerous
on your own.
Well, Sakisaka's
by himself.
No, you don't understand.
Sakisaka will be fine.
Huh?
Because he's my teacher.
He can't lose!
You're getting
on my nerves.
Who's this?
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
I was following Haseo.
So where exactly
have you been?
Umm...
I was just...
I'm going back home.
Hey, that guy who just
came by TaN's home area...
wasn't that Haseo?
He's already switched guilds?
Well the Twilight Brigade
is nothing compared to TaN.
What did he say?
Why did you call me here?
I would like to hear
your opinion on something.
My opinion?
There's an item that doesn't
exist in the game specs.
Without it you can't
get to the place
where the Key of
the Twilight is.
An item that's not in the specs?
Whaddaya say about that?
Interested?
So?
So what?
So what if
I have no opinion?
Do you think
it could be true?
Who knows?
Aren't you a member
of the Twilight Brigade?
The Isn't the Key
of the Twilight
what you're hunting for--
I don't care what
info you have to offer...
this has nothing
to do with you.
Oh, it certainly does,
you just don't see it.
Tawaraya leaked
the information directly.
Ender, you know
what to do next, right?
Yes.
Go for the weakest link.
Done.
Who exactly... are you?
What's this?
Are you
interested in me now?
Well why wouldn't I?
You're the one sniffing
around the Brigade
and PKing everyone,
aren't you?
So, what?
But why?
I've got the same agenda
as you and your friends:
finding the
Key of the Twilight.
Hey, there's Haseo!
Good luck to ya,
little boy.
Haseo!
Oh! What happened?
You look really grim!
Is something the matter?
Please leave me alone.
And here I was I was
worried about you.
Sissy!
Stupid PKer.
[NASUBI] It's very rare
to see you in town.
Shut up!
If you have time
to talk to me,
you have time to look
for some information!
Idiot...
Is that...?
Haseo, what do you think
about your information
on the item that's
not in the specs?
I think...
we all need to take a closer
look at this item either way.
We should try to find out
if it has anything to do with
the Key of the Twilight.
Well then, investigate it.
If your information is correct,
then you take credit for it.
Haseo smiled!
No, I didn't.
Now, there's something
I want you all to do.
What is it? What is it?
There's an item
called a "Virus Core"
that's not in the manual.
I want you to search for it.
Virus Core?!
Do you know about it?
No.
Shino, show
them where to go.
Okay.
We need a Virus Core.
It's a special item
found only in a Lost Ground.
So, you mean it's a rare item?
Exactly.
Let's spread out
and look for it.
Well, how many
of them are there?
I'm not sure how many,
but I think
there's more than one.
What does it look like?
I believe it's
shaped like this.
It's really small.
I wonder if
we'll find them.
You'll never know
what's to be discovered
if you give up even
before you start looking.
That's right!
And I'm gonna be
the first one to find it!
Do you really think
we should separate?
After all, we are
being targeted, you know.
Sakisaka,
you worry too much.
Whatever.
Then I guess
I'll go have a look.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah but,
I really don't think
we're gonna find that
item in a place like this.
No matter what
information there may be,
the Twilight Brigade
always tries.
You wanted to check out the
information, too, didn't you?
What is that?
I don't know what that is.
But that's okay.
Things we don't understand
surround us constantly.
It's true, and not
just in the game world.
It's the same in the real world,
at home or in school,
or at your part-time job.
Because of the unknown,
there's the joy
of understanding.
And because
of the mysterious,
there's the excitement
of discovery.
Even if you don't
always know the rules,
just enjoy your role
and take things as they come,
and everything
will fall into place.
There would be
nothing left to enjoy...
...if we knew everything.
Tabby!
The woman who PKed me!
Hei.
Our running speed
should have increased!
So, hurry!
It doesn't matter
how fast you run...
...or how far you go.
You're all trapped like mice.
It's so quiet.
Where did she come from?
She showed up as if
she was waiting for us.
Haseo, did you do something?
Me? Why would I?
Well, I've been
hearing rumors.
People are saying
that you switched to TaN.
Tabby!
What?
Something isn't right!
Well, where did you get the
information you gave to Ovan?
What's all this "defeat Ovan"
stuff you've been talking about?
Fine, whatever.
Haseo.
No one's gonna complain
if I quit this guild, right?
Tabby, that was way too much.
Goodness me.
Oh, this isn't like you.
Are you feeling down?
Hey, Haseo?
Would you buzz off?
If you need anything else,
don't hesitate to call me.
So it's true...
Haseo is...