[PC 11A] Isn't that the guy
from the Twilight Brigade?
[PC 11B] He's that PC
the Brigade and TaN
were fighting over.
[PC 11C] It's amazing that they
destroyed such a huge guild.
[PC 11D] I can't believe
TaN cheated like that.
[PC 11E] Didn't they fall
into the Brigade's trap
and get exposed?
[PC 11F]
Yeah.
Hi, Haseo!
Isn't it amazing?
Haven't you heard?
We're really famous!
Yeah, you know what...
[SAKISAKA]
Shut up!
Hey, um...
--Huh?
Where is...
...you know.
I, uh...
Where is Shino?
It's weird, she hasn't
logged in yet today.
But when she does,
you know what?
I bet she's gonna be surprised
now that we're famous!
[TABBY]
Speak of the devil.
What's that?
[TABBY giggles]
Has Ovan been in
contact with you yet?
Not yet.
Don't you think this
is just a bit weird?
[HASEO]
Stop yelling!
I wasn't talking
to you, Haseo.
Didn't we all fight for
the Key of the Twilight,
and didn't we all
believe in Ovan?
Why did he take off
and abandon us?
What's the matter,
Teacher? Are you angry?
I just wanna know
where he went.
[HASEO]
Well, I'm here.
What is it you want?
I wanted to say sorry.
Jeez, something feels
wrong to hear you apologizing.
Yeah, y'know...
I guess you may be right.
In exactly thirty
minutes' time,
my account will be suspended.
So then I'm guessing they
know that you're involved?
Makes sense.
I am the face of TaN.
I won't run away.
[HASEO]
That's honorable.
Iúm not trying to be
honorable, you know.
You could say...
[HASEO]
Hm?
...I have something you
might call merchant's pride.
I take responsibility
for my dealings.
That's all there is to it.
I gotta admit, I learned a
pretty good lesson this time.
By the way,
if I were to ask you,
would you be able
to do me a favor?
Well, it depends.
I'm not gonna say
yes to just anything.
I think you're aware
of the distorted
graphic anomalies
that are unique to
the Lost Grounds, aren't you?
They look like triangles.
[HASEO]
The scars?
[TAWARAYA]
Yeah.
I've never seen a
cheat like that before.
[HASEO]
And?
Since Revision Two,
TaN has always been
at the leading edge
of any new trend
in The World,
and that has consistently been
the reputation of our guild.
"Signs".
I've given it some thought, and
that's what I'm gonna call them.
Signs?
[TAWARAYA]
Yeah. If someone asks you,
I'd like you
to tell them that.
[HASEO] You really
think someone would ask?
[TAWARAYA] They're like
omens or harbingers.
I named them with that in mind.
The day will come
when Signs will be
the topic of
conversations everywhere.
I guess my time is up now.
I understand.
See ya later.
But if his account
is being suspended...
...there's never
gonna be a "later".
[SAKISAKA] I wanna know if Ovan
found the Key of the Twilight.
Haven't you heard anything?
[SHINO] I can't
get in contact with him.
[SAKISAKA]
You have no idea
how tired I am
of hearing that, Shino.
[SHINO] There's no use
getting all worked up about it.
No use getting
worked up about it?
What if he got greedy
and took it for himself?
No, Sakisaka.
Do you really think that...
...Ovan would do
something like that?
Have patience.
But how long can we wait?
There's a time limit
for everything, isn't there?
Even with Ovan?
[BSET]
Hey, you.
Come with me.
You shouldn't be
so cheerful right now.
But why not?
Why not?
Ovan hasn't come
back yet, has he?
Are you telling me
you're not worried?
Don't you wonder where he is?
But Ovan's
hardly ever around.
Besides, Shino is here!
You have got to stop
acting like you're still
in junior high school.
You're completely wrong!
I'm not a junior anymore!
I'm a senior, silly!
[TABBY]
Haseo!
[TABBY laughing]
What's up?
I was warning her about
being way too cheerful.
Can you please
take her with you?
I didn't do anything
that deserves a warning.
Anyway,
what are the chances that Ovan
might be coming back here?
I really couldn't say.
You're probably better off
asking Shino about that.
It's not that easy.
That's why I'm
asking you instead.
I'm gonna go back
and ask Shino myself!
Hey, hey,
let go of me! Ow!
Oh...
You know those scar-like
graphic distortions
in the Lost Grounds?
People are starting
to call those things Signs.
I didn't realize
they had a name already.
Yeah, it only just
happened recently.
Just in case someone asks you,
I'd appreciate
if you told them that.
I guess I can.
[TABBY]
Haseo, come on, let's go.
Signs?
Some kind of symbol...
[GORD]
Now where did you go?
I guess it's my turn.
I think the moment's
come for me to move on.
[PHYLLO]
I see.
[GORD] It doesn't look like
Ovan's gonna show up again.
It's about time for me to quit.
[PHYLLO]
Oh?
I have to say that
since we first met,
you've done a lot for me.
I'm flattered,
but it was nothing.
Besides, how else is an
old man supposed to kill time?
But Phyllo,
won't you be lonely?
No, The World is
just like a playground.
Everyone will leave eventually.
Just like leaving
the playground at night.
Sooner or later, one by one,
everyone goes home.
Everyone eventually leaves, huh?
Do you think you're
going to be all right?
What do you mean?
I'm talking
about the real you.
That's the reason why
I have to quit this game.
I just can't keep running away
from my real life problems
here in The World.
Running away.
Ahhh.
I know the first thing
I need to do is redeem myself.
[PHYLLO] You know,
you can make a fresh start
not only on the 'net, but
in the real world, as well.
Wouldn't that be nice.
Teacher!
Where're you goin'?
[HASEO]
What's up with him?
[TABBY]
Hey there, Shino!
What happened?
Sakisaka just
stormed outta here.
He'll be okay.
Did something terrible happen?
Whatever happened,
it's something you guys
don't need to worry about,
so you really don't
have to look so serious.
[NAOBI]
So you're here, as usual.
Well anyone can find me
here easily, can't they?
Are you sure you want
to be wandering around
after what's happened
to your guild?
[NAOBI]
I'm not concerned.
[PHYLLO]
I see.
There are so many
rumors going around,
I thought you might
be a little concerned.
[NAOBI] Today's the
last day for this character.
I think I understand.
None of these
rumors would matter
as long as you leave
this character behind.
So, what brings you
out here today?
[NAOBI] I have something
to tell you, old man.
All right then,
let's go somewhere else.
[NAOBI]
Forget about Ovan.
He can't come back anymore.
Ovan, please...
I'm pretty sure Teacher
hasn't logged out
of the game or anything,
but he still doesn't seem
to have replied to me yet.
How are we supposed
to find him
when he's just
wandering around?
I just don't know.
What do you think we should do?
I would totally call him
if I knew his phone number.
But I don't actually have it.
Do you know it, Haseo?
Come on, if you don't
know Sakisaka's number,
why would I have it?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[HASEO] It's probably
better if we wait at home
instead of wandering around.
[TABBY]
Aww!
What was that for?
t's so cute you wanna
be with Shino that much!
I what?
[TABBY] I saw that look
in your eyes earlier,
when you were gazing at Shino.
You're not being serious.
It's a CG you're looking at.
No.
I can tell you were gazing at
her fondly through your display.
Well, you're pretty awesome,
but you can't really
replace Ovan, can you?
What do you mean by that?
I mean at the moment,
you're unable to support Shino.
What?
You're trying to tell me that
you could support her yourself?
Probably...
...I'd say probably not.
[SHINO] It's very rare
to see you here, Phyllo.
[PHYLLO]
You haven't seen him
since he disappeared
from that place?
No.
[PHYLLO]
Has he been in contact?
[SHINO]
Uh-uh.
[PHYLLO]
I see.
So it's true.
Hold on just a second.
What do you mean by that?
Please, Phyllo.
You're going to have to
tell me exactly what it is
that you know.
[TABBY]
Sakisaka wasn't in town.
I think we should check out
the Lost Grounds.
[HASEO]
Or you could send him an e-mail
telling him to come back.
I mean, he is
wandering around, right?
[TABBY]
I told you he's not replying.
[HASEO]
Well just keep trying, then.
Oh! Hey, Bset!
You're a little early.
[BSET]
Mmm-hmm.
[NASUBI] The rumors say all
the Lost Grounds have them.
So this is one of them, huh?
[BSET]
They're called Signs.
[NASUBI] I wonder if
they're gonna be used
in a new event or something?
So. What is it you want?
[NASUBI]
Oh, yeah.
It's about Gord.
I understand now.
He had a feeling from the
beginning that it was a trap.
I just hope that he
isn't suffering too much.
Even if he's being held captive,
I know he's strong and I'm
certain he'll come back
and rejoin his friends soon.
In the meantime,
with the way things are,
we'll need to stick
together more than ever.
But I know I can't gather
the Brigade by myself.
So Phyllo, who was
the one that told you
Ovan isn't coming back?
It was Naobi, wasn't it?
[PHYLLO]
Why do you ask?
You met Ovan...
...before I ever did, and
you know more about him.
So I just figured that you were
acquainted with Naobi as well.
Maybe it's just
women's intuition.
It's not like I thought
you and Naobi
are working together
or anything like that.
Don't worry.
I just can't believe it.
It's as I feared.
Ovan wasn't able to find the
Key of the Twilight, was he?
[PHYLLO]
Well, that's the way it is.
I'm sorry.
It'll be okay.
At least I think so.
Anyway, most importantly,
I need to tell everyone
what's happened to Ovan, right?
[PHYLLO] Ovan, is it really
true that you're gone?
What are you two doing?
You guys aren't waiting here
for Sakisaka, are you?
[Actually, we were
thinking about
where to look for him.
You don't need to
worry about that anymore.
I'd like you both
to go home right away.
Why? What's up?
Did something happen?
I have some important
news for everyone.
What is it?
Let's just go home first
and I'll tell you there.
[SHINO] After examining
various reports...
I've come to the conclusion
that we were wrong
and the Key of the Twilight
does not exist.
Huh?
Are you trying to tell me
there's no such thing?
[SHINO] "Does not exist"
means exactly that.
What about Ovan?
He ran into
a little trouble.
I don't think we'll be seeing
him around here for a while.
Trouble or not,
it doesn't matter.
So regardless, there's
no way he's gonna show up
if there's no
Key of the Twilight.
He can't face us again
after all we've been through.
Well then, whaddaya
suggest we do now?
No, are you saying Ovan
isn't coming back anymore?
You're not saying that
we're gonna be disbanded
like TaN was, are you?
No, I'm sure that
after a while he'll return.
So don't worry about it.
Yay! We'll just
have to wait, then.
Besides, we're already used to
Ovan never being around anyway!
Right?
Are you an idiot?
Can't you see that
it's different this time?
If there's no
Key of the Twilight,
then there's no way
he'll show his face.
Just forget about it.
Don't say that.
[SHINO]
He'll be back, for sure.
Prove it to me!
[HASEO] There's no use
fighting about it.
Besides, arguing like this
is not gonna change
anything, is it?
[SAKISAKA] Excuse me,
but I'm gonna go cool off.
Sakisaka, wait.
[TABBY] I'll go
check on my teacher!
[SHINO]
I'm sorry.
Shino, there's no reason
for you to apologize.
But its my...
Thank you, Haseo.
Listen, you don't need to
thank me for anything, either.
I think I'm going to
log out for the rest of the day.
Teacher, wait for me!
[SAKISAKA groans]
Teacher, wait.
I said wait!
Why can't you
just leave me alone?
Why?
I just want some time
on my own so I can think.
But what could there be
to think about?
More than you could ever know.
Are you gonna leave, too,
just like Bset and Gord left
the Twilight Brigade before?
[SAKISAKA]
Huh? Of course not.
Okay! Let's go!
Why don't we head back home?
Let's go! Come on!
Enough!
Why are you always so
blindly and annoyingly cheerful?
Don't think it's
because I want to be!
[TABBY sobbing]