[TAIHAKU] I'm sure we've
met before, haven't we?
[OVAN]
No, we haven't.
But then again,
there isn't anyone
who doesn't know
of Taihaku from Icolo.
Haseo?
[HASEO]
Shino!
Shino, hang in there!
Repth.
Repth!
Talk to me...
Hey! Shino!
[phone ringing]
--[phone ringing]
--C'mon Shino,
--answer your phone!
Come on!
Please, please hurry!
Shino!
Shi...
Shino.
[HASEO]
What is this?
What the heck is this?!
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit!
Dammit!
[PC 16A]
Hey, are you going?
[PC 16B] I told you,
I have no interest
in going to a pointless
official event.
Did he say...
...official event?
[PC 16C] But I heard
if you drop out once,
you can't get back in.
What's that all about?
[PC 16A] That doesn't
sound like an event.
[TABBY]
Oh! Uh...
Hey! Huh?
Hey, you're that girl.
From the other day.
Tell me about
this official event!
You mean the Forest of Pain?
That's what it's called?
I'm surprised you didn't
get an e-mail notice for it.
I dunno what it is,
but there are players
who have already entered
and are talking
about it on the forum.
Oh.
My mind's been occupied
by lots of other
things these days.
[KUHN]
It's a week long.
During that time, you're
supposed to do something
at the deepest
area of the field.
[TABBY]
Do what, exactly?
[KUHN] I dunno.
Only those who reach that point
will find out.
[TABBY]
So no one knows yet...
[KUHN] The enemies
are unusually strong.
So far, no one
has finished it yet.
In the forum, some people
have been saying
it's impossible to finish.
Whoa.
Why don't you
read about it yourself?
I gotta get going.
I'm busy trying
to set up a new guild,
and I've gotta back to it.
Oh! I'm sorry.
I see.
So...
Kuhn is setting up a new guild.
[PHYLLO]
Ah, you came.
I just wanna
ask you something.
[PHYLLO]
About Shino and the guy?
Yeah, I came here
to ask you about Tri-Edge.
[PHYLLO]
What about him?
I want to meet him.
[PHYLLO] You know,
you can't just meet him
because you want to.
[HASEO] Tell me about
the time you met him.
Because if he appeared
somewhere other than
in the Lost Grounds
where those Signs are,
something must be up.
That doesn't change anything.
Please, Phyllo.
[PHYLLO]
Haseo...
I think you really need
to forget about Tri-Edge.
How could I forget
when things are like this!
Shino's still unconscious
in the real world, you know.
I'm aware of that.
The doctors have no
idea why she lost consciousness.
You visited her?
[HASEO] And because
they don't know the cause,
they don't know
how to treat her.
That's why I need to
track down Tri-Edge right now.
I understand,
but the answer's no.
Which one of them would you
like Saburo to follow?
[YATA]
Who is the real one?
They both joined
at the same time.
[PI]
Haseo.
Tabby.
Neither of them have
enormous amounts of data
like Ovan.
And earlier?
Anything strange about them
when you were with TaN?
No. I would have
said something.
[YATA] I know you
reported everything.
Even then, you never failed
to catch the small details.
However...
Tabby, for one, has had
contact with the unknown.
Haseo was there, too, though.
[YATA]
Well, we'll leave Haseo alone
for a little while longer.
If he manages to contact
Tri-Edge on his own,
there's no doubt
it'll be very interesting.
For now, I'll let you decide
how to move the pieces.
[PI]
You can count on me.
What are you doing?
Hello?
So you're here.
[PI] I came exactly
when I said I'd be here.
This is actually a
really nice place, isn't it?
Don't you think it'd feel good
to sleep in a place like this?
[PI]
A nice place?
Is it really necessary
for us to meet here?
[PI] I just don't
want to meet in town.
Even though TaN isn't
even around anymore?
[PI]
Did you read my e-mail?
I did.
You mentioned the beast girl.
But it's strange.
How come?
[SABURO]
There's more going on
with the Black Adept Rogue
kid, don't you think?
You really should consider
just following orders.
Maybe quit thinking
so much and do as I ask.
[SABURO] But the other kid
seems so much more interesting.
It's as if my older brother
stole my favorite snack
that I'd been saving
to enjoy later.
[PI]
I don't get it.
But be sure to make contact.
Contact only?
[PI]
Right.
If you can do that properly,
I'll let you know
what to do next.
[SABURO]
Okay.
I hope she understands me.
[HASEO] There has
to be a Sign somewhere.
I need to find it.
[TABBY] I heard the
Forest of Pain was started
in order to find someone
to defeat Tri-Edge.
[PHYLLO]
What do you mean?
[TABBY] Apparently the CC Corp
is going to ask the winner
to take him out.
It's kinda like a competition
between the players,
and the prize is
a chance to fight Tri-Edge.
[HASEO]
For real?
Sorry, but that
simply isn't true.
If they wanted
to remove Tri-Edge,
all they would have to do
is terminate his account
or delete his character data.
[TABBY]
Oh, I see.
That's why it's a lie.
Don't let the rumors
get the better of you.
[HASEO] C'mon, why don't
you just tell me already?
What do you
want him to tell you?
[HASEO]
Mind your own business.
Don't talk to me
like that, Haseo.
[HASEO] It has
nothing to do with you.
What do you mean it has
nothing to do with me?
What the heck do you know?
I care about Shino.
I wanna do something, too.
There's really nothing
you can do here.
So don't bother
yourself with Shino,
'cause it's none
of your business.
[PHYLLO]
Don't say that!
Come with me.
I already came
here to look.
So is there something
here after all?
With the way
you are right now,
it won't do any good
for you to meet Tri-Edge.
You're mistaken
if you think he'll care
even a bit about what you say.
What do you mean by that?
He's completely unpredictable.
He'll attack you first
without saying a single word.
[HASEO] You ran away
from him, didn't you?
Personally, I don't
know of any players
who could defeat Tri-Edge.
Well we won't know until I try.
Fool!
But I have to try.
[PHYLLO]
If you try and fail,
you'll end up
becoming a Lost One.
The risk is too high.
But he spared you.
Isn't that right, Phyllo?
[PHYLLO]
Well he might not spare you.
Please don't start a fight.
Come on, let's
get on with it, please!
Haseo!
[PHYLLO] How can you
possibly match Tri-Edge
if you can't even
begin to stand up
against a
Harvest Cleric's attack?
[HASEO]
Uh, I...
[PHYLLO]
Don't you see now?
You're dead!
Come on!
I'm the only survivor.
As far as we know,
I'm the only one
who has gone up against him
and lived to tell
about his true strength.
Yeah, so what?
[PHYLLO]
Don't you want to help Shino?
You're gonna regret this.
Watch your mouth,
or I'll make you eat
your words, little boy.
Is that all you got?
Shut your mouth!
[PHYLLO chuckles]
[PHYLLO] It's not like I
don't understand how you feel.
But what happened to Shino
is not your fault.
But it is my fault.
[PHYLLO]
Don't make me repeat myself.
You're a child
who just won't listen.
You can't see
anything around you.
Both of you please stop it!
[YATA]
So there is a survivor.
Well, Phyllo,
What is your connection to Ovan?
[PHYLLO]
Do you get it now?
If you meet him,
you'll end up the same
as everyone else.
I'm not gonna give up.
Even if it means dying.
You listen to me!
Talking about death
is not something
you should take lightly!
But I told her...
...I can take care
of things now.
That's very nice of you,
Haseo.
I have to do something.
[PHYLLO]
Do something?
You can't do anything with
your current skill and strength.
You better go cool off.
Haseo!
[PHYLLO]
What's the matter?
Phyllo, that's enough now.
You should let Haseo
do what he wants.
You don't need
to speak for me.
Tabby.
I'm sure Haseo is
capable of doing it.
[PHYLLO]
If he can't even take me on,
how can he possibly--
Even so, violence can't
be a solution to everything.
But in this case,
I'm afraid it is.
[HASEO]
Forget it.
I understand what
you're trying to get at.
I just need to become stronger.
I can't tell if they're
actually friends or not.
I'm sorry about earlier.
[PHYLLO]
What for?
I think I might've
gotten in the way.
[PHYLLO] Didn't you
do it because you thought
it was the right thing to do?
I couldn't just stand by.
Now if only Haseo
would stop thinking
he can do everything
all by himself...
I hope things will become
a lot clearer for him.
[TABBY]
What? Sorry.
I think my system is
lagging just a little bit.
[PHYLLO]
Nevermind.
This is nothin'.
Let's go back.
They're too strong here.
[PC 16B] It's nothing
compared to the Forest of Pain.
[PC 16C] The rumors say there
are ridiculously strong monsters
that keep appearing without
giving you any time to rest.
[PC 16A]
Sounds horrible.
[PC 16C]
Not really.
Apparently if you clear it,
you become exponentially strong.
But that's a rumor, too.
[PC 16B] Where do you get
that kind of information?
Is that right?!
[SABURO]
Can I sit beside you?
Huh?
[TABBY]
Who are you?
Well, my PC data is public,
so why don't you
have a look at it?
This is nice, huh?
Must be good
for people watching.
Uh, I was wondering...
You are a girl, aren't you?
[SABURO]
Yeah. Why?
Saburo's just a weird
name for a girl, that's all.
Oh my gosh, that's such
a huge stereotype!
What's a stereotype?
[SABURO]
There are boys with names
like "Leslie"
or "Tracy", you know?
[TABBY] Do you think there's
any with the name Louise?
[SABURO] Louise is my
great-grandfather's name.
I'm kidding.
[TABBY laughs]
Haseo should be--
I'm just here
waiting for my friend.
He's supposed to
pass by here soon.
Oh.
He's amazing.
He always lives up to
everyone's expectations.
What about you?
What about me?
I'm just useless.
If you say
you can't do it,
you really won't
be able to, you know.
But if you think
everything's gonna be okay,
it will be okay.
It's a lot like
a stew that will last
for days and days
if you keep it simmering.
Oh!
What does that mean?
Looks like...
...I am alone.
[PI]
Excuse me?
Who are you?
Can I speak to
you for a moment?
All I have to do
is get stronger!
Stronger!