[TABBY] Hey!
[PHYLLO] You're like
a sulky 12-year-old,
mad because he
didn't get his own way.
What are you
going to do next?
Steal a bike and
ride away with it?
If you don't like being
suspected then log out.
And if you still
don't like it, then quit.
After all, it's just a game.
Am I wrong?
Maybe we can't
trust Haseo anymore.
You think?
But at least I have
my teacher--Sakisaka!
Are you listening?
[SAKISAKA]
Huh? Uh... yeah.
You're acting strange.
What do you mean?
Are you going as well?
Uh, going where?
To see the meteor shower!
Huh?
It was on this morning's news.
It's something that only
happens every few decades.
And they said
there are gonna be
lots and lots
of shooting stars!
Huh?
You don't know about it?
Uh... no I don't.
I guess you're not
a teacher in the real world.
You should pay attention
to the Eastern sky tonight.
I live in a small
bachelor apartment.
I probably
won't see anything.
[SHINO] After I tell
the others about their mission,
I'll be taking a break
and logging out for today.
[OVAN] Alright.
I appreciate all your work.
The doctor at the hospital
says my recovery
is going smoothly.
But I'm afraid I still
have much more ahead of me.
Ah, I see.
I was thinking that
perhaps it would be best
if I give this mission
to Tabby and Sakisaka.
Haseo is
rather hard-headed,
and he can't cooperate
under these circumstances.
I'll leave it up to you.
Thank you Shino.
[TAWARAYA]
Alright.
[ENDER]
Working again?
My goodness, you never
take a break, do you?
For now, just
keep picking away
at the Twilight Brigade's
soft spots!
Well, see ya.
Picking away huh?
More like slashing!
If you think you've
been falsely accused,
you need to prove
your innocence on your own.
Otherwise...
You could log
out early today
and admire
the stars--and relax.
[HASEO]
Stars?
You haven't heard?
Tonight you can see
the meteor shower.
I'm not interested.
Okay, if I can
see the stars,
I'll contact you
and let you know, okay?
I don't care.
Anyway, I'll let you know.
Okay. Whatever.
We have to go
treasure hunting again?
Shino's calling us!
We have to go now!
What are you doing, teacher?
I almost left you behind!
I can't believe it,
this has got to be
the worst timing ever.
Sorry Tabby,
I'll just be another minute.
You go on ahead okay?
I'll catch up!
Hey, wait a second!
Oh! That was quick!
Don't just stand there.
Go on, have a seat.
What do ya want?
So, have you
made up your mind?
Have you decided
whether or not
you're going to join me?
Is it Haseo or me?
Tell me, which
one of us is it
that you want
or need more?
I'm the one who
asked the question.
Just answer me.
Don't be so
dim-witted, kid!
Huh?
If I were to come across
2 pieces of jewelry
on the ground,
which one would I pick?
The answer is easy!
I'd have to pick both
of them, of course!
Come on, don't tell me
you haven't any
business sense at all?
Business, huh?
Think about it
very carefully.
But remember...
It only took
a single e-mail
to get you to come
all the way here.
You wanted to see me
that badly, didn't you?
Did you know?
That you can see
the meteor shower tonight?
Come on, you're talking
about in the real world?
It has no value
and time is money!
Do you honestly
think I have time
for petty distractions
like a meteor shower?
I see.
Aww, really?
Sorry.
Hi!
Hey, what took so long?
Haseo won't be joining us
on this mission.
That doesn't matter to me.
Yeah, it doesn't
matter if Haseo comes
as long as
Sakisaka's with us. Right?
So, what are we
supposed to be doing here?
Today we're going to
focus on other fields,
instead of just
the Lost Grounds.
I want you to see if
you can find the Virus Core
in ordinary places,
like this dungeon.
Sounds like fun!
I'm gonna find every
one of those Virus Cores!
Teacher?
Alright!
Let's all three of us go in
there and find 'em together!
Actually, Shino
needs to take care
of some stuff
in the real world,
so today it's
just gonna be you and me.
I'm sorry.
Shino's probably
going on a date
to watch the meteor
shower with her boyfriend.
What?
I know! I know!
I bet Shino's pretty
and kind in person, too!
I'm sure men in the real
world can't leave her alone!
Tabby, that's not--
Don't worry about it!
Just leave this
to Teacher and me.
We can handle it.
You go enjoy your date
with your boyfriend!
Okay, let's go Teacher!
Hey, stop
calling me that!
Why can't I call
you that, Teacher?
How about Brother Sakisaka?
Not that, either!
Well, we'll be able
to see the stars soon.
Are you logging out?
Of course.
I haven't seen a meteor
shower since I was very young.
Bye for now.
See ya.
You don't even
have the slightest bit
of romance in you,
do you kid?
I wonder where it could be?
Oh Teacher, I always wanted
to do something like this.
It's like we're real
treasure hunters, isn't it?
Yeah, I guess.
What?! Tabby?
I really saw it!
I saw the meteor shower!
What?
You're talking
about the real world?
Can you see it from
your house as well?
Let's go.
Hey!
I asked if you can
see it from your house.
I told you that
it'd be impossible
to see it
from my apartment.
But Teacher,
it's so beautiful.
Am I going crazy or did
something just sparkle?
There you go,
you can see it!
No!
There's something
over there!
Be careful, Tabby.
I'm okay,
'cause you're with me!
Besides, we'll be
done here soon, right?
Sooner than you think.
There's a meteor shower
happening right now!
Really?
I can't see it
from my house.
Shooting stars...
I didn't even think of that.
They look like
falling stars!
I heard you the first time.
Now, you need to--huh?
What is this?
It's so pretty!
Huh?
Amazing!
No!
Tabby, send Shino
an e-mail now!
But didn't Shino say that
she was gonna log out today?
It doesn't matter--
it's an emergency.
Just send it
to all members!
Okay!
Alright...
Here I come.
What is this?
Tabby!
Tabby, let go, quickly!
But I can't
seem to get it off!
We need help right now.
Somebody has
to answer us!
I'll try e-mailing
one more time.
Tabby, don't be an idiot!
Just forget about it and
just worry about yourself!
Aw geez, I don't get it!
Why do we always have to
get screwed over like this?
Forget it Teacher,
you gotta move away from
me or you'll get hurt too!
No, I won't leave you.
It's the Player Killer!
You have to
run away, Teacher...
Or we're both gonna die!
Shut up!
Damn it.
Teacher, I'm so sorry...
Tabby, be strong!
Haseo... why you?
Hey Haseo!
You're late, as always!
I was just
about to log out.
You guys are a nuisance.
Haseo!
You're gonna wish
you did log out.
Haseo!
Hey little boy.
It's been awhile.
Oops, my bad.
Sorry to give you away!
Maybe I should have
said "Nice to meet you?"
to save you
from embarrassment.
Teacher she's lying...
She's lying... right?
You don't know her...
Do you, Teacher?
Please tell me
you don't know her ...
Answer me!
Boy Sakisaka,
you're a disappointment.
I thought you could've
actually been useful to us.
Oh, just deal with it.
I'll do you last.
Now wait here,
you little traitor.
I'm gonna have fun
with you first!
Help Teacher!
We have to help
Haseo or he'll die!
Come on!
I won't kill
him that quickly!
Don't worry about that!
You should be more worried
about the terrible things
I'm going to do
to you, silly girl.
Teacher!
Did you finally muster
up the courage,
or do ya wanna die?
Not just yet.
Did you happen to know
that you can see the
meteor shower tonight?
I'm not interested.
Of course you aren't.
If you had made
it easy for me
I would have
simply PKed you.
Now I'm gonna
make it hurt!
Sakisaka.
Careful Teacher!
Listen Tabby,
I have a confession.
You convinced me
to take a look outside,
and I can see
the meteor shower.
Teacher.
Are you okay?!