Haseo!
[PHYLLO] How can you
possibly match Tri-Edge
if you can't even
begin to stand up
against a Harvest
Cleric's attack?
I'll get even stronger.
I'm gonna save Shino
no matter what.
[PI] So you don't want
to go somewhere private?
[PHYLLO]
There's no need for that.
[PI]
Why?
[PHYLLO]
Because I have
nothing to say to you.
[PHYLLO] I don't care
how many times you ask.
I'm not going to explain my
relationship to that girl.
[YATA] Tell me, how long
have you been sitting here?
You've encountered the girl.
After observing you
sitting still for some time,
she approached you
out of curiosity.
Perhaps she thought
you were a stuffed animal
sitting there doing nothing,
like a little toy
in a store window.
It seemed she was
enjoying this world
by chatting with you
while passing the time
waiting for someone else.
Isn't that right?
[PHYLLO]
Who gave you the right
to pry into other
people's memories?
If I'm not
entirely mistaken,
it was through her
that you and Ovan met.
But is that
all there is to it?
[PHYLLO] If you've
already checked me out,
then there's no need
for me to tell you.
[YATA] I want to know
the exact details
of your relation to Ovan.
[PHYLLO] There's nothing more
than what you just said--
I keep things simple.
[YATA]
Oh?
[PHYLLO] I'm sorry
you wasted your time.
Hey, where are you going?
[PHYLLO]
It's dinnertime.
Master Yata, he--
Don't worry about it.
So this is it.
[TABBY]
I hope Haseo is doing okay.
[SABURO]
Don't forget it's only a game.
You don't have to worry so much.
[TABBY]
Yeah, you're right.
I thought Haseo
hated official events
and things like that.
He usually tries to avoid them.
[SABURO]
What about you?
[TABBY]
Me?
[SABURO]
Yeah, why don't you do it?
[TABBY]
It's too hard for me.
I can't do anything.
[SABURO] If you think it's
too difficult, it will be.
Don't you agree?
Unless you act on your own,
nothing will begin.
[TABBY]
Maybe, but--
[SABURO] You know,
there have even been people
who are afraid of heights
who fall in love with
skydiving after trying it.
I don't care anymore.
I don't wanna
talk about it.
[ringing sound]
I gotta go now.
Yeah, whatever.
You'll get
cobwebs in your head
from moping around
like that, you know.
Come on!
It's totally unnecessary
for us to meet in this place.
[PI] You're involved with
other player characters
aside from me,
so from now on,
we have to move very cautiously.
You want me to do
something that might be risky?
[PI] Nothing that would
break the rules.
So, what am I doing next?
The Black Adept Rogue
from the Twilight Brigade.
You remember him, don't you?
[SABURO]
Haseo, right?
For your next mission,
I want you to follow him
into the Forest of Pain.
I see...
So that one's your
favorite snack after all.
Look, just do your job
and stick to my orders.
You just want me
to make contact with him?
I'll be giving you
additional instructions
once you've accomplished that.
Now I know how a Beagle feels
when he's used for hunting.
Don't you think?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
You know the Forest of Pain?
It seems like a
really terrible place.
[PHYLLO]
Hm?
I heard it's full
of high-level monsters
that you don't see in
any of the normal areas.
[PHYLLO]
Mmm.
There's no weapons shop,
and the only items you get
are the ones you pick up
when the monsters drop them.
In other words,
you can't just go in there
and expect it to be
an everyday walk in the park.
I wonder if Haseo
went there to get stronger.
Well, what other
reason could there be?
I really hope he's okay.
I wouldn't worry about it.
If he simply went there to get
stronger and raise his level,
I'm sure he'll be fine.
But if he wants
to fight Tri-Edge,
that won't be enough.
Yeah, well right
now I'm wondering
if there is anything that
I can do to help him out.
Who did that?
Was that you?
What's the matter?
You got something
against healing spells?
Well don't expect
me to say thanks.
[SABURO] This is a Lost Ground,
so even if you clear it,
nothing will happen.
What did you say?
Well, that's just
one person's opinion.
But I don't think
I'm necessarily wrong.
I really think
you're wasting your time.
[HASEO]
I won't know unless I go.
[SABURO]
I guess that's true.
[HASEO]
Who are you?
[SABURO]
Saburo. Nice to meet you.
What, aren't you gonna
cast a stereotype on me?
[HASEO]
Huh?
[SABURO] Don't you think
my name doesn't sound girly?
[HASEO]
Whatever, I don't care.
[SABURO]
You're a good guy.
[HASEO]
What's that supposed to mean?
[SABURO] Why are
you doing this event?
Don't you think it's weird
that they haven't
revealed the final reward
for clearing this
Forest of Pain?
I think the CC Corporation
opened the event to save face,
because they couldn't do
anything about the Lost Grounds
that appeared so suddenly.
It doesn't seem too far-fetched.
After all, this game does
have a mysterious autonomy.
[OVAN]
That's right, Haseo.
It's important
to recognize this game
has a very mysterious autonomy.
Autonomy?
Neither the
system administrator
nor any other entity
can control it.
In fact, parts of The World
are completely governed
by the rules of the game itself.
'Kay, that's enough.
Just stop following me.
What an interesting kid he is.
[OVAN]
So you came.
[OVAN chuckles]
Hey you, have you
ever heard of Tri-Edge?
[HASEO]
Do you know something?
[SABURO]
No.
Is he really a player character?
I mean, rumor has it that PCs
destroyed by him
are lost forever.
[HASEO] Are you saying he's
a non-player character?
[SABURO]
That's impossible.
If he was an NPC,
then CC Corp
would delete him
or take countermeasures.
[HASEO]
Then what is he?
[SABURO]
An A.I.
[HASEO]
A.I.?
[SABURO]
Yeah, artificial intelligence.
That's why CC Corp
can't do anything.
[HASEO] Can't they just
erase the program?
Aura.
Have you heard of her?
Aura?
There used to be
a statue of a girl here,
but that was a
very long time ago.
A girl?
[SHINO]
Yes, Aura.
That is the name
they used to call her.
The statue in the cathedral.
Yeah, so?
[SABURO]
Half right, half wrong.
There's the statue,
but apparently,
there was once
an A.I. called Aura.
And they couldn't erase it?
[SABURO]
Probably not.
People wrote about it in the
forum from the old revision.
[HASEO] Does that A.I.
character still exist?
[SABURO]
I dunno.
But if there aren't
anymore rumors,
then it's probably gone.
I think Tri-Edge
appeared in place of her.
Like a father
begging for forgiveness
because his daughter
ran away from home.
[HASEO]
In place of her?
What for?
Huh...
I wonder.
I guess you're gonna
have to ask him yourself.
[TABBY]
Oh!
Hi! What's goin' on?
Hey, what are you up to?
Me? I'm not doing anything.
I think I'll
pass on your offer.
Alright, then.
If you change your mind,
don't hesitate to contact me.
[TABBY]
Hm?
[KUHN] Oh, well
I just started a guild
and I was looking
for members, and I was
asking him if
he wanted to join.
Hi, nice to meet you.
I'm Seisaku.
My name's Tabby!
A guild? What kind?
I guess it's like a
support guild for beginners.
Hangin' out with
you the other day
made me realize that's something
I'd be capable of doing.
A support guild
for beginners, huh?
[KUHN]
It's called Canard.
Wanna come join us?
[KUHN]
Are you listening?
Oh.
No, thank you.
Okay, well I
gotta get goin' now.
Something he can do, huh?
But is there
something I can do?
[HASEO]
What did you come here for?
Sightseeing.
[HASEO]
What?
Wait a second.
You're that...
[HASEO]
Hmm?
What?
[HASEO] You're clear if you can
get to the deepest area, right?
[TAIHAKU]
I haven't been there yet,
so I still don't know.
[SABURO] It's unthinkable
that you'd get a reward
just for reaching
the end of the forest.
[HASEO]
You stay out of this.
[TAIHAKU]
What do you think, young lady?
[SABURO]
There is no clearing it.
This event's a scam.
[TAIHAKU] There may be
some truth in that.
[HASEO]
Can you clear it or not?
[TAIHAKU]
You may think that you can,
or you may think
that you cannot.
But then which approach is
more interesting as a game?
That question is
for each of us to decide.
It does.
You must play this game
with the assumption
that it does exist.
That is why we are known
as the Twilight Brigade.
[TAIHAKU]
Did I say something strange?
[HASEO]
No.
Well, I'm going
to keep moving on.
Sure.
If it's possible,
let's meet up again
in the deepest area.
Yeah.
So why didn't you
take up Kuhn's invitation?
You mean my reason
for not joining Canard?
Yeah.
Mainly because
it's my impression
that it's not only the beginners
who need help finding
their way in The World.
What exactly do you mean?
I realize that in a game
where there are lots
of Player Killers,
it becomes very challenging
for beginners to last.
But from what I've seen,
I'd have to say it's
toughest for intermediates.
Really?
For example,
if you're equipped
with valuable weapons,
a PK would
target you for sure.
That makes sense.
And until they've
obtained their objective,
they'll continue to PK.
There are a lot of
players like that.
They always go
after a certain class.
The ones that really need help
are the intermediate players,
because they're the ones who
aren't really strong enough yet.
Have you decided what it is
that you want to do, Tabby?
I'm really not sure
what I should do.
In fact, I don't even
know what I can do.
That's not what I'm asking.
What is it that you
want to do for yourself?
I really want to save Shino.
And I want to be there
for Haseo, too.
But I'm...
Master Yata,
I recently made an analysis
on what happened
at Briona Gwydion.
And what exactly
did you discover?
I came across some
data that can't be analyzed.
So it's Ovan.
Yes, I believe it's him.
Anything else?
There's evidence that
he fought against Tri-Edge.
Well!
[PI]
A Sign?
When did that happen?
You know, I'd rather go solo.
But I think you're gonna
get to the deepest area first.
Is that why you're here?
Well, since there's
only one day left
'til this event is over,
and since I came
here as a sightseer,
I'd like to
see some action.
You know what they call
people like that, don't you?
[SABURO]
Hm?
Parasitic.