It's frustrating, isn't it?
What's frustrating?
I'm pretty sure Haseo
is out there doing his best.
Yeah... I'm certain he is.
And still, there's
absolutely nothing
I can do to help him.
I don't even know if he's
really okay right now.
You can at least go
and ask him how he's doing.
Don't you know?
[PHYLLO]
What?
You can't send
messages, even short ones,
to the Forest of Pain.
[PHYLLO]
Is that so?
Yeah.
You can transmit
once you're in there,
but not from the outside.
[PHYLLO]
Really?
[TABBY]
It's strange, isn't it?
I think that's why
everyone's saying
this event isn't normal.
[PHYLLO] Yes, but once
you're inside the forest,
you can contact him, right?
[TABBY] Well, if I go in there,
I'll just get in the way.
[PHYLLO]
You think?
You know what?
I wanna go in and
ask him how he's doing.
And also, I wanna be
helping out somehow.
But no...
Haseo--He wouldn't like that.
I understand.
That is frustrating.
Well...
Just three hours 'til it's over.
And it looks like it's
going to be a long three hours.
I can't be dealing with
these worthless monsters.
I gotta get to the deepest
area before I'm outta time.
There's no end to this!
Get out of my way!
I will get stronger.
I have to.
I will get stronger!
Their moves are simple,
but I'll be dead for sure
if I get hit. Great.
Anyway, I lost Taihaku.
I wonder what I should do?
[ringing noise]
[PI]
What's the situation?
Hey, how come you can e-mail
me from outside the forest?
[PI] I'm the one
with the questions here.
You're not beside
Haseo, are you?
[SABURO] Is that why
you came into the forest?
What's going on?
[SABURO shrieking]
I don't know.
I can't seem to move.
I've actually started
thinking about quitting.
What?!
This isn't some joke!
[SABURO] Don't you
think it's as useless
as putting an unopened can
of food in the fridge?
[PI]
I don't get it.
Anyway, keep some distance
and continue watching Haseo.
Okay.
But it's difficult to
keep up with him--
[beeping noise]
Hm? She just says whatever she
wants and drops out like that?
Hm?
[TAIHAKU]
Is this the end?
Are you here?
Yeah. Sorry.
I was...
...just studying
for tomorrow's class.
There's still two hours
left in the event.
You're welcome to take
a break any time, you know.
[TABBY]
But what about you?
Well, you know
me, my dear--
I'm always here like this.
[TABBY] I've been curious
about that for awhile.
So do you just sit there
looking at your monitor
until someone comes
and talks to you?
No, silly.
I read books, magazines,
and play with my dog.
[TABBY]
You have a dog?!
A Schnauzer. Do you
know what that is?
[TABBY]
Yeah! The bearded dog, isn't it?
That's right.
He turned twelve last month.
In human years, he's
eighty-four years old.
He's an old timer
just like me.
Really?
I never thought
you were that old.
Anyway, doesn't your
wife ever get mad at you
for being logged into
the game all the time?
[PHYLLO] Oh, it's just
the cats and the dog now.
Oh.
I see.
I hope you don't think
I was prying too much.
[PHYLLO]
Don't worry about it.
Well, I'm gonna go
read the forum for a bit.
[MALE VOICE]
I... shall ask you a question.
[MALE VOICE] Is my daughter
safe and sound?
[MALE VOICE]
Answer me.
I apologize,
but as far as I know,
I'm not acquainted
with your daughter.
However, I hope and wish
that she is safe...
...and well.
[MALE VOICE] I shall bequeath
that sword to you.
Oh, hey.
So I thought you quit.
Says who?
Oh, you know.
Well, don't worry about it,
because I plan
on quitting, too.
Get outta here.
You're wasting my time.
Listen, if you're gonna quit,
then why don't you just
leave me alone and get going?
[SABURO]
You can have these.
Recovery items and stuff.
You'll need them.
Since I'm gonna leave,
they're useless to me now.
Don't expect a thank you.
That's fine. But instead,
my member address
comes part and parcel
with this little gift
I'm so generously giving.
Kind of like an advertising
banner on a free server.
I get enough spam already.
[monster growling]
Anyway, these monsters' special
attacks are pretty tough.
A word of advice to you
is to try and avoid
any unnecessary fighting.
[HASEO] Why don't you
mind your own business!
That kid is sizzling water
dancing on a piping hot skillet.
Can he clear the event
before he completely evaporates?
That was an awesome metaphor!
[PC 18A] Hey! Someone cleared
the Forest of Pain!
Oh!
[PC 18A]
Taihaku of Icolo cleared it!
How can I avoid fighting?
Is she an idiot?
It's not like these guys
are ever gonna let me get by!
[PI] I'm shocked you
actually quit your assignment.
Let's go somewhere else.
I need you to explain
yourself right now.
Just tell me.
Who are you?
[PI] What are you
trying to get at?
Your appearance
and speech are different,
but I can tell who you are.
You're Ender, aren't you?
Why are you asking me now?
[SABURO] I've been wondering,
you're good at role-playing.
But which is your true
character, Ender or Pi?
Naobi's here under a
different name, too, isn't he?
He disbanded a huge
guild without hesitation.
But he's still lurking
around somewhere in the game.
Isn't that weird?
[PI] Well, you got that
character out of it, didn't you?
Oh yeah,
I suppose so, but...
I wonder, how did you know
I wasn't with Haseo
in the forest?
I get it.
I had a feeling
you followed me
'cause I hung around
even after I said he quit.
But you know,
I only thought he left.
I just lost sight of him
'cause he wanted
to get away from me.
But it turns out
he was still there.
[PI] You're the one
who didn't obey orders.
You know what?
I've had enough.
[SABURO] There's something
suspicious about you.
I don't like it.
I'm logging out.
[PI]
Don't think I'm going to--
[SABURO]
Forgive me for it?
That's fine.
Do what you want.
As long as it doesn't
stir up a hornet's nest,
everything will be okay, right?
[PI] You don't understand
anything, do you?!
[SABURO]
Then explain it to me!
I have to keep my mouth shut
and deal with enough pointless
work in the real world.
And to be honest,
that's the last thing
I wanna put up with here!
Taihaku of Icolo?
Well, yes,
I sort of know who he is.
Then there's no mistake.
I heard people
talking about it in town
and I checked
it in the forum.
He's the one.
Who finished the challenge?
[TABBY]
Yeah.
What kind of person is he?
Icolo is a group of people
who have a strong pride
in their own strength.
There are only four members.
Out of the four,
Taihaku's at the top.
[TABBY] He must be
very strong, then.
I wonder if Haseo's okay?
[PHYLLO]
Tabby?
[TABBY]
Yeah?
Be patient for now.
[TABBY]
Huh?
You won't always be
rewarded for working hard.
Sadly, the reality
is not that simple.
The idea of your efforts
always being fruitful
is really only a fairy tale.
Even so, Haseo
is doing his best.
Right now he's probably
all by himself in the forest.
Therefore, all
we can really do
is wait and hope for the best.
Yeah.
No matter what the outcome,
I'm certain Haseo
doesn't want to regret
having not tried his very best.
That's why he's fighting
on his own in the forest.
He's not looking for any reward.
I expect everything will
play itself out in the end.
Just believe in Haseo.
[TABBY]
Yeah.
[PHYLLO]
I'm going out for a bit.
Come on!
I didn't come all this way
to get a stupid weapon!
[HASEO screaming]
Master Yata?
[YATA]
He disappeared?
That's impossible!
Isn't it?
[YATA]
Interesting.
This is where
impossible things happen.
Only in The World.
[MALE VOICE]
I shall ask you a question.
Is my daughter safe and sound?
What are you talking about?
[MALE VOICE]
Answer me.
How should I know?
Wh-Who are you?
And who the heck
is your daughter?
[MALE VOICE] I shall not
bequeath those swords to you.
[choked screaming]
[PHYLLO] Even someone
like you, Taihaku of Icolo,
had a hard time
in the forest.
It was tougher than I imagined.
[TAIHAKU]
What kind of man is he?
[PHYLLO]
Huh?
[TAIHAKU]
It took me a long time
to realize you are the
same Phyllo from before.
Which reflects the depth
of our relationship.
Nevertheless, you,
who many call the
Mac Anu ornament,
or the teddy bear
on the bridge,
came all the way here.
There must be someone in the
forest you are concerned about.
That's right.
[TAIHAKU]
I won't push the question.
I hope your friend
comes back safely.
That player's
taken quite a beating,
so it's a good time to quit.
Well, that's my
opinion, anyway.
Hold on.
[PHYLLO]
Huh?
I've explained the
severity of that event.
And yet, you're perfectly fine
with letting your
friend fight alone?
How can you be so
dismissive of him...
...or her?
He's a boy.
It doesn't seem right
that you would disregard
that boy's earnest efforts.
There's something much worse
waiting for him once he
finally clears the forest.
Something truly terrible.
[TAIHAKU]
I don't know.
But if that's
the road he chose,
then no one has the right
to say anything about it.
[PHYLLO]
A game is a game.
The Net isn't
the same as reality.
And it just doesn't seem right
to link the two together,
no matter how tempting.
[TAIHAKU] Is that
what this is all about?
Right.
It's not an issue
I can figure out easily.
[PHYLLO] That large
sword you obtained...
Was it worth the
hardship in the forest?
[PHYLLO]
I am sorry.
I must be a bother.
[throat clearing]
[SEISAKU]
Pardon me.
--[TABBY] Huh?
--[SEISAKU] May I join you?
Hi there.
Why are you here?
You were really anxious
and worried about Haseo,
so I just thought
you might be here.
I see.
Is he still working
his way through the forest?
Yeah.
When he finally gets back,
I want to be the first
one to congratulate him.
I can at least do that.
I know it might
bug him a little,
but I thought that
I'd wait here anyway.
That's all it is.
[SEISAKU]
Haseo must be very happy.
What?
To have such a
wonderful friend.
I don't know about that.
Haseo doesn't think
of me as his friend.
[SEISAKU]
Is that so?
[TABBY]
He thinks I'm annoying.
I don't understand why
you'd support him, then.
I see.
That's what I wanna do.
And that's what I'm able to do.
I think I'm finally
beginning to see it now.
It's just a feeling, though.
[ringing noise]
[ANNOUNCER 18A] Attention:
This area will be closed
upon the completion
of the event.
[YATA]
Any results?
He's definitely still
in the game somewhere,
but I can't pinpoint
the location.
[YATA]
It doesn't matter.
Once the event is over,
we'll soon find out.
[ANNOUNCER 18A] Warning:
This area will be deleted
upon completion of the event.
Users currently in this area,
please take the nearest
platform to town immediately.
Three minutes
to area termination.
Where is he?
Don't worry about him.
[ANNOUNCER 18A]
The countdown to area closing
can be seen in your sub-window.
Attention: Users
currently in this area,
--take the nearest platform
--Let's go back to the town.
--to town immediately.
--If the area disappears,
--Three minutes
--we're in big trouble.
--to area termination.
--We can't, not yet.
[TABBY] Haseo's still
in there by himself!
[SEISAKU]
Tabby!
[ANNOUNCER 18A] Warning:
Two minutes to area termination.
Users in this area,
take the nearest platform
to town immediately.
[SEISAKU]
Tabby... We have to go!
But he's...
[TABBY shrieking]
Haseo.
[HASEO growling]
[YATA]
Pi.
[PI]
Yes?
[YATA]
There's no doubt now.
He possesses the Factor.