Hey, are you okay?
What happened?
[MIDORI]
Tri-Edge!
Tri-Edge?
Hey did you hear
there's a Player Character
that got away from Tri-Edge?
Of course!
It wouldn't be
such a big deal
if everyone who
encountered Tri-Edge
simply became a Lost One.
Yeah, that's true.
So, who was it?
It wasn't the
Black Adept Rogue, was it?
No, it was
a Blue Edge Punisher.
Really?
[IITA] I think the one that
got away is that stuffed animal,
the one who always sits
at the edge of the canal.
[PILOCCIO] Yeah it could be,
but he's a Harvest Cleric
and he's more brown than blue.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I'm going to the port
to gather some information.
It's definitely
this Player Character.
[YATA/NAOBI]
So she escaped Tri-Edge.
She looks like
a rare character.
[PI/ENDER] That one
is legitimate, though.
Tri-Edge.
The Lost Ones.
A series of
mysterious phenomena.
Is this PC
just another player
that got swept up
with the tides,
or is there something
more at play here...?
What would you
like me to do?
Well, Pi.
Yes.
Think like Ovan would think,
then act like Ovan would act.
I see.
[TABBY]
Where's Phyllo?
[TOUTA/TAWARAYA]
Hi there!
I haven't seen
him yet today.
Oh.
He's usually here,
so it seems kinda weird
when he's not around.
Is something going on?
You don't have
time to talk do you?
Sure.
I was wondering...
If I were Shino, what
would I be doing right now?
I've been thinking
this whole time
about what it
is that I can do.
But no matter
how hard I try
I can't be like Shino.
So, I should just do
my best with what I can do.
And what would that be?
I'm actually not too
sure about what to do.
That's why I came
to get Phyllo's advice.
I think that you
should be a guild master.
Huh?
There are things
you can do with a team
that you simply
can't do alone.
Why don't you just
make a guild for now?
Then see where
things go from there.
It's really too bad...
but like I said,
you guys are no match for me.
Come on.
How can you really know that
for sure until you try us?
Well, maybe the
rumors are false.
[HASEO] The word on the street
is that you know Tri-Edge.
Master Yata.
This is beyond anything
we could have expected.
Is that all you've got?
[SABURO] Man! That punk!
I can't get that
guy out of my head.
Don't think you can scare
me with your brute strength.
I am who I am because
I'm able to wield this power.
What do you want?
Your "hit-me-if-you-can"
service.
I get one minute, right?
Is that what you came for?
How much?
If you become a repeat customer,
the first time is free.
So that's why
I started up a guild,
but I still don't
know what to do.
[SEISAKU] Personally, I think
you should take things in order.
Huh?
First, what do
you want to do?
I really wanna help Haseo.
What do you
mean help?
I think that maybe
I'm capable of healing people.
Not just Haseo, but I'm
certain I can revive others
including those people
who've been killed by Haseo.
Healing is not a job
for a Tribal Grappler.
But I could... if I carried
the maximum number of items.
There's no way
you can get
enough money to do
something like that.
I guess.
But you did ask me
what I want to do.
True.
Alright,
let's move on.
Next you have
to figure out
what you need to do
in order to achieve that.
I don't know.
I'll give you
a hand.
Huh?
Listen I'll do whatever
you need me to do.
So why don't we do
our best together?
That's all you get.
Your free minute is up.
So I guess that's it.
Master Yata,
look at this.
I've just finished
investigating
the details
of her player log.
It's here at
Briona Gwydion.
Give me the gist of it.
Please wait,
there's one more.
This is the log of
Tri-Edge and Ovan's battle.
Same time, same place.
In other words,
she witnessed
the battle between
Tri-Edge and Ovan.
She was there
the entire time.
Very interesting.
But that event is
already in the past.
Tell me.
What are you going to do
with this information?
As you said,
I will think like Ovan
and I will act like Ovan.
Welcome back Pilo.
"Hit-me-if-you-can."
Huh?
The survivor Midori has a
"hit-me-if-you-can" business.
I don't get it.
Basically,
for the right price
anybody can try
and attack her.
No, I still
don't understand.
She puts a bounty on herself
and gets other players
to pay to challenge her.
If they can hit her once,
they get a reward.
If not, she keeps the cash.
It really must be
the end of this world
for a business like
that to be profitable.
Is it really
successful?
It seems to be.
Welcome to our shop!
Where's Touta?
Do you know him?
Well, yes.
The reason I'm here is
to offer some information.
Sorry, but we don't buy
or sell information here.
I'm not trying
to sell information.
I said "offer," didn't I?
Well that
probably won't work.
There's nothing more
expensive than what's free.
It's not like
I'm not offering
the information
to you anyway.
Touta should be the one
to make that decision,
don't you think?
Yeah, I guess...
Alright then... so...
you wanna hear it?
Hi!
Hold on a minute--
You can have
this PC body back.
What do I need to do?
If I log out, will that
do the trick for ya?
Huh?
You did say you
wanted to use it.
So I'm giving it back now.
What are you up to?
Nothing at all.
Don't you think
it's much better to have
a cheap crappy car that
I can use whenever I want,
than a fancy expensive car
that could be taken
away at any moment?
I actually
understand you for once.
So what are you
planning to do
with your cheap crappy car
that you can use
whenever you want?
I'll give you a hint!
Haseo.
I think I'd just like to
watch him a little bit more.
I don't need it.
What?
That Player Character
is useless anyway,
you can have it.
But why?
Like I said,
it's become useless to me.
Didn't I just tell you
I don't need it anymore?
No matter how long
you keep sour milk,
it's not like you're ever
gonna drink it again, are you?
Even if it ferments
and turns into cheese,
that's not
the original intent--
I take back
what I said
'cause I'm sick of
your stupid metaphors!
Really?
That's right.
I'm giving you
that PC body.
Don't come
near me again!
So those are the conditions
for me to be free?
Sometimes it's like dealing
with a grouchy five-year-old.
What a brat.
Hi guys!
How's business coming along?
Oh, hey Touta!
Pilo and I got some
amazing information!
Yeah it's about
the player who witnessed
the battle between
Tri-Edge and another PC.
You guys know who it is?
And we also learned that
the player in question
actually fought
with Tri-Edge too!
So I guess that would
make them a witness as
well as a survivor then.
Got a name yet?
Midori.
She isn't logged in
right now by any chance?
She has a very
strange business.
A so-called
"hit-me-if-you-can" business.
Who's the source
of this information?
Some girl.
Her name's Pi,
and she has pink hair.
You know her?
She seemed to know you.
If you know her you should
show her your appreciation.
Plus she seemed
to know that we were
looking for that
information already.
I'll be back in a bit.
Why? Why not me?
How can Midori
come across Tri-Edge
when I've been
hunting for him?
You're the one with the
"hit-me-if-you-can" business.
And you are...?
Well you can call me
the tip-off man, Touta.
So, you're here
doing business too.
There's something
I wanna ask you.
What?
You have to tell me
if you know Tri-Edge.
It's that again, huh.
What do you mean "again"?
You're actually
not the only one
who's wanted to
know about that.
You're pretty
popular, aren't you?
Word on the street has it
that you're not only a survivor,
but in fact
you're also a witness.
Isn't that right?
What are you suggesting?
What I'm saying is
that you faced Tri-Edge
and barely got
away with your life.
That's true, but I'm not
sure what you mean by "witness."
You encountered
Tri-Edge once before
and saw
something interesting.
A battle between Tri-Edge
and another player.
[gunshots]
The information
you have is correct.
I've encountered Tri-Edge
on more than one occasion.
Or perhaps I should say
I saw him one of those times.
So is that all
you wanted to ask me?
I wanna know more
about the player
that was
fighting Tri-Edge.
I don't think
I could tell you.
I was watching
from far away.
Then what
can you tell me?
I don't remember.
He seemed to know...
It was a guy then?
He knew his way around the
Lost Ground "Briona Gwydion."
I understand.
You won't get any more
information out of me,
no matter how hard you try.
That's all right.
What is this?
Just a little something
for the information.
Are you stupid?
After someone answers your
questions out of kindness.
You must know
the purpose of this
was only to show my
gratitude for your kindness.
I don't want it.
Then I guess that means
I still owe you one.
See you later.
Will Haseo fight
with Midori again?
Yes.
This time it won't be one of her
"hit-me-if-you-can" services.
She'll be fighting
with all of her strength.
Will it shake him up?
It won't hurt to try.
That's how Ovan
would think, isn't it?
Hey! Are you ready?
Yup!
That character...
I'm afraid you'll
have to get rid of it.
How come?
The impact of
first impressions.
A guild should
be well-rounded.
Are you saying I
should remake myself?
That's right.
Your vocation again?
Blade Brandier.
Then you should change your
vocation to a Harvest Cleric.
What?
How about me?
You've already
opened a guild
so you can't
change your character.
Oh yeah.
Hold on, so it's just the two
of you doing this together?
Uh, yeah.
What is the minimum
number for a party?
Um, three?
You're missing
one person.
One more, huh?
How about Phyllo?
Are you serious?
I guess not.
Of course.
If Phyllo was gonna
do anything like
that I'd have
him help me first.
Just one more person.
One of my
"real world" friends
said he's gonna
start playing soon.
I'll see if Hideyo
wants to join us.
Hideyo?
That's a very plain
name isn't it?
And then...
Uh-Huh?
I'll ditch this character.
Nya?
It's okay.
Alright, now that the members
have been decided,
you need to start thinking
about your catchphrase.
Catchphrase?
If you wanna be
remembered in the future,
you're gonna have to come up
with a mission statement.
I see.
So what are you
gonna call your guild?
Paw Pad Squadron!
Paw Pad?
What, you mean like...
the little soft parts
of a dog or cat's paw?
Yeah.
Is it bad?
[giggles] Perfect!
Sorry I'm late.
So what is it?
There's a Player Character
who defeated
Tri-Edge at Briona Gwydion.
What did you say?
Are you telling me that
Tri-Edge isn't around anymore?
I really don't
know about that.
Who was it?
Who and where is
the guy that defeated him?
I don't know.
My informant
doesn't seem to remember,
and there's no way I can
dig for the information.
Tell me who told you this.
Midori.
The player who has the
"hit-me-if-you-can" business.
I know her!
She's a survivor and
a witness or so I heard.
No, it would be
the other way around.
She was able to survive
because she has
witnessed him before.
That seems to
be more logical.
Where are you going?
Where do you think?
Well I guess that
was to be expected.
What do you
want this time?
You!
What do you
know about Tri-Edge?
I already told you!
I've heard that you were there
when Tri-Edge was defeated.
And if I was?
You'd better think harder
and tell me about
the one who beat him.
Get lost, I don't
want to remember.
I can smell
death in the air.
I wish you were good enough
to take Tri-Edge's place
and fight just like him.
You're not bad.
You're actually
pretty good.
Tell me... who
exactly are you?
I told you, I run a
"hit-me-if-you-can" business.
He was pretty strong
you know, that Tri-Edge.
Guess you're just
not strong enough.
Whatever.
Apparently the Factor
is still dormant.
What is this?
I can't even defeat the one who
barely got away from Tri-Edge?