Meow!
[TABBY screams]
[SAKISAKA]
Calm down.
Just pretend they're a pack of
monsters and it'll be a breeze.
Okay!
Save your victory
celebration for later.
[HASEO]
There's so many of them!
Where's Ovan?
[SHINO] No word.
I haven't heard anything.
We'll go to the
next floor and regroup.
We're gonna run out
of recovery items soon!
Just a little longer!
Remember, the enemies in
front of us are insignificant.
If Ovan finds the
Key of the Twilight,
then victory is
ours for sure.
Got it?
[SAKISAKA]
Exactly!
Even though they've
got us cornered,
we've got the upper hand.
[OVAN]
Shino.
It's time!
[OVAN]
I must go now.
Take care of the rest.
Ovan!
What?
Nothing to worry about.
Just a little longer!
Keep it up!
--Okay!
--Right!
[NAOBI]
I was waiting for you.
Finally, it's time
to commence phase three.
[OVAN]
Just as I thought.
This is what it's all about.
[NAOBI]
Oh?
You predicted this
and yet you still came?
Or are you too proud
to admit defeat?
[OVAN]
I had to come.
That's why I'm here.
That's all there is to it.
[NAOBI]
That's unlike you.
Or is it?
Searching for the Key of
the Twilight at all costs
is very much like you.
However, never doubting
the assumption
that the Key of
the Twilight exists
is not like you at all.
[OVAN]
The Key of the Twilight.
At one time, it took the
form of a forbidden bracelet.
And yet another time,
it was the ultimate AI.
You were the one that
told me it once existed.
[NAOBI]
Yes. We did talk about it.
Not only does this
game have a realm
that's beyond the reach of
the system administrator,
but the program itself
has its own autonomy.
It's a mysterious game that can
change its shape on its own.
That is "The World".
In it, there exists an entity
that is trying to
steer our universe
towards a better future.
That is the
"Key of the Twilight".
You also told me
it was the key
that will bring about
the twilight of dawn.
[NAOBI]
Yes.
That is also why I prepared
this scenery for you.
[OVAN] So, twilight is
the dimming light of dusk
and it's also the
breaking light of dawn.
[NAOBI chuckles]
[NAOBI]
Ovan, have you forgotten?
I also told you that since
the second revision of the game,
the Key has been lost.
[OVAN]
How could I forget?
Anyway.
I'm still very much inclined
to continue my search
for the supposedly mythological
Key of the Twilight.
If it had existed at one time,
it could still exist now.
And I will focus all
my energy into finding it.
[NAOBI]
Why?
Let's just say it's personal.
[OVAN]
But enough talk.
Why hasn't Ovan
tried to contact us yet?
[GORD] You're still
naïve as ever, Sakisaka!
What was that?
Honestly, has Ovan
ever been good at
communicating with people?
No, he hasn't!
Why are you guys so
mindlessly enthusiastic?
You look like you're
enjoying yourself, too!
[GORD]
Shino, go on upstairs.
We should be able to
take care of things down here.
[BSET]
I agree with Gord.
Why don't you go check on how
things are going up there?
[SHINO]
No, I should stay here...
Haseo, you have to go.
[SAKISAKA]
It doesn't matter who,
somebody has to
go check on Ovan.
C'mon, Haseo.
Please just listen
to Shino, okay?
But why do I have to go?
Because, Haseo...
...you are Ovan's future.
Would you just go already?
[NAOBI]
It's no use.
You can't do anything here.
You've determined your fate
the moment you passed
through those doors.
This is gonna be fun!
Boy, what a showoff.
He...
...he's so dreamy!
What?
Someone, come in and help me!
See, I told you he's a showoff.
I'll help, too!
[OVAN] What are you
going to do with me?
[NAOBI]
I'm not going to harm you.
I'm merely interested
in the mystery
behind that PC body of yours.
[OVAN]
What kind of nonsense is this?
It's just some
Player Character data.
[NAOBI]
Don't pretend you don't know.
Aren't you aware of
your PC data size?
It's enormous--bigger in
scale than a whole area.
From my understanding,
what you've achieved
simply can't be done.
It's impossible.
I want to know exactly what
you did to make that happen.
I'm going to examine
you thoroughly.
That has been my
intention all along.
[NAOBI]
There's no use in struggling.
I'm restraining your PC body to
find out what makes you tick.
Mission accomplished.
Retreat with me, slowly.
[HASEO]
Ovan!
Where'd he go?
Ovan.
[PHYLLO] I just gave
you a little push.
You decided on your own
to go and help the Brigade.
There's really
no need to thank me.
I know.
But I still wanted to
show you my appreciation.
I guess sometimes
these things happen.
Haven't you heard?
There's rumors spreading around
about the Twilight Brigade
actually finding
the Key of the Twilight.
I hear it all even
when I try my best not to.
It's kinda funny, isn't it?
In fact, we didn't
actually find the Key.
Then Ovan disappeared,
and no one's seen or
heard from him since then.
[PHYLLO] And TaN's secret
service put on a big show.
[BSET]
Yeah.
There's that, too.
And the fact that TaN had
secret operations all along
is now out in the open.
[PHYLLO] You know, everyone
who's playing this game
just wants a story that
makes some kind of sense.
By talking about it,
it makes them feel like
they're part of the action.
That's how the rumors
continue to spread.
That's all there is to it.
[BSET]
You sure keep your cool.
Well, when you're
as old as I am,
nothing really comes
as much of a surprise.
It all just gets boring.
Phyllo, I think you might
be wrong about that.
[PHYLLO]
Is that so?
Think about it.
If you don't move
and you're always here,
no surprises
will come your way.
You taught me the importance
of acting on your gut feelings.
That's why I wanted to
thank you for your help.
Thank you, Phyllo.
[SAKISAKA]
I'll ask you one more time.
Ovan wasn't there at all?
Cut it out already!
You saw it too, Sakisaka!
There was absolutely positively
no one on the top floor.
That wouldn't have been the case
if you hadn't let him go.
What are you talking about?
[SAKISAKA]
Well, it's too weird!
Where did Ovan go?
[SHINO]
Settle down, Sakisaka.
We all checked it out
just to know for certain.
There was no structure
that would transport anyone,
no scars or anomalies.
It's obvious that place
was a complete dead end.
[TABBY] It's true,
because the only way
we were able to get out
of that place was to reboot.
[SHINO] And I'm sure you
performed a thorough check
for any strange openings.
You know, like the ones in
the Hulle Granz Cathedral
where you got
trapped in the walls?
[TABBY]
Yeah, there weren't any. Right?
[SAKISAKA]
Yeah.
But still--
So if you think
about it logically,
there's absolutely no way
on earth that Ovan could
have moved from that place.
[SAKISAKA]
Unfortunately, I disagree.
[HASEO] Yeah, if he
would've rebooted like us,
he easily could've gotten
back to the town gate.
[TABBY]
I guess so, but why?
Would Ovan purposely
disappear like that?
[HASEO] I'd like to
ask him that myself.
Well...
...maybe Ovan wanted to
keep the Key of the Twilight
for himself or something...
I doubt it.
Ovan's not gonna
sell us out like that.
I don't think he
would do that, either.
Besides...
Yeah, but still...
Why the heck hasn't any one
of us heard from him yet?
[SHINO] Maybe it's not that
he isn't contacting us...
What if he wants to, but can't?
We have to be
a little more patient.
Okay?
Did you think I was Ovan?
No. You just surprised
me a little bit.
About Ovan,
you're friends with him
in the real world,
aren't you?
I know I really
don't have the right
to ask about
your relationship,
but have you tried
contacting him in reality?
It's been useless.
I have tried to reach him,
but I got no reply.
I see.
I'm so sorry.
Huh?
It's just...
I have to stay strong.
Know what, Shino?
You are staying strong.
Can I stay like this?
Just for a while.
There's a mountain
of complaints--
I can't handle them all.
You will handle
them, you idiot!
You're not a real man if you
can't deal with all the claims!
Why don't you think of it
as a personal quest
to prove yourself?
But...
I don't wanna hear any more
"ifs", "ands" or "buts".
Those are just pitiful excuses
and I've heard more than enough!
[PC 10B] There's someone
here who insists on seeing you.
You don't get it, do you?
[PC 10B] Someone called Shino
from the Twilight Brigade
has requested
a meeting with you.
From the Brigade?
Welcome!
What is your business with TaN?
I'm going to skip
the formalities
and go straight to
the reason why I'm here.
I'm asking you,
please give Ovan back.
I'm pretty sure I don't have
that kind of merchandise.
You're not looking for any
information, are you?
I heard you're
a character who plays
the role of a
merchant in this world.
Where's Ovan and what
have you done with him?
I wonder...
[SHINO]
Are you pretending not to know?
Or maybe they kept
you out of the loop
and didn't tell
you anything.
Alright, if you're
such a know-it-all,
what else do you know?
Ovan gave me data that
reveals all the dirty things
TaN's been up to.
For example, the fact that
you have a secret service
working under you.
And all the activities that
the system administrator
turns a blind eye to...
Believe me, I do have it.
[TAWARAYA]
Wait.
What do you mean,
"turns a blind eye"?
I see.
So you were just another
player unwittingly being used.
I think you should ask Naobi.
I know you like to make
deals, so let's make one now.
Guarantee the safe
return of Ovan,
and I promise
I won't do anything.
If you don't comply,
the data I have on TaN
will be made public
without hesitation.
So do we have a deal?
[TAWARAYA]
Well now...
That's not a deal.
That's a threat.
[SHINO] Either way,
I'll only wait twelve hours.
Get me Naobi, now!
And until I say so,
stop taking orders.
And cancel all the ones
you've already taken.
Why are we doing that?
[TAWARAYA] TaN is on a special
holiday effective immediately!
No matter what, you have to
go and locate Naobi!
Okay, I get it...
Right now?
Don't ask questions
when you already
know the answers.
Get a move on, go!
[HASEO]
What do you want?
[GORD] Nothing much.
I just wanna talk.
If it's nothing,
then why am I here?
What do you think, Haseo?
Has Ovan found the
Key of the Twilight or not?
I guess at this point,
it doesn't really
matter anymore, does it?
Well I think it does.
Listen, I'm fairly
certain you never really cared
one way or the other if the
Key of the Twilight existed.
You were just happy Ovan
gave you a place in this game.
You've got to admit
that was the only reason
why you were searching for the
Key of the Twilight, wasn't it?
Why would you say
something like that?
You wanna know?
'Cause it was the same for me.
[HASEO] Then what was all
that "defeat Ovan" stuff?
Only our initiation
to the Twilight Brigade
was the same...
but our exits
will be different.
Still, because our
motives are similar,
I know what you're up to.
Don't go thinkin' you can
understand me so easily.
See ya later.
Say hi to Ovan for me.
[PC 10C] I heard the Brigade is
waging an all out war on TaN.
[PC 10D] It's the other
way around, isn't it?
[PC 10C] Of course,
TaN is a much bigger guild.
But it is the Brigade
that's waging the war.
[PC 10D] Maybe the
Key of the Twilight
gave them some
sort of advantage?
[PC 10C] They probably just
got fed up over something.
[ENDER] It seems the
girl from the Brigade
gave the administrator data
that proves that TaN has been
involved in illegal activities.
[NAOBI] So, that's what
Ovan was preparing.
[ENDER] Well, don't you feel
that might make things easier?
[NAOBI]
Why?
[ENDER] Because TaN
is no longer needed now.
[NAOBI]
That's true.
It simplifies things
if TaN is disbanded
because of its activities.
[ENDER] These PC bodies will
become useless pretty soon.
[NAOBI] I never felt much of
an attachment to this character
in the first place.
Yeah.
[NAOBI] Well then,
I'll continue examining Ovan.