[TOHTA]
So you're alright.
Well then, Haseo, what happened
to all of your weapons?
I'm not too sure.
[TOHTA] I guess that's what it
means to be initialized,
doesn't it?
[TOHTA]
Oh, nothing.
I'm glad you're safe.
[TOHTA]
Haseo!
Phyllo is not coming back.
[HASEO]
What?
[TOHTA]
He didn't actually quit,
but I guess
it's the same thing.
[HASEO]
I don't get it.
[TOHTA]
We have no privacy here.
We need to go somewhere else.
I have something to tell you.
[OVAN]
Shino.
It's starting now.
[TABBY]
I need to report to Shino.
What's that?
Oh, it's nothing.
No way.
Phyllo was in the
game the whole time
just hangin' around.
He never did anything
other than sit on the bridge
staring at the water.
That's right.
He was always there.
And he was worried about you
until his last days.
[HASEO]
But why--
At the very end,
Phyllo specifically asked
me to look out for you.
I just don't understand.
Really?
[HASEO]
Knowing he had cancer
with only eight
months left to live,
how could he continue
to calmly play the game?
And he was worrying about me?
He should have been worrying
about himself, not me!
[TOHTA]
He couldn't help it.
Phyllo...
Phyllo had taken care of
everything around him
and all he had left to
worry about was you.
[HASEO]
But--
What would you do
if you were told you had
just eight months to live?
Do you know?
What?
[TOHTA]
Would you be anxious?
Or depressed?
Or would you frantically
try to achieve something
so that you could
leave behind a legacy?
Those are about
the only possibilities
people like us
can imagine, right?
Well, I... I guess.
[TOHTA] Phyllo didn't
choose any of those paths.
During his last few days,
he wanted to
live them out calmly,
as though nothing had changed.
And that was how
he wanted to live his life.
Calmly, huh?
While it is true Phyllo
knew he was dying,
he also knew that those of us
who aren't dealing
with an illness
could very well die
tomorrow or the next day
in an accident.
"Now who do you
think is the one...
...who'd feel regret
in the end?"
Yeah, Phyllo said
that with a chuckle.
He told me that
you're trying to do
too much by yourself.
And that he was overly harsh...
...and regretted it.
I guess.
To be honest,
I mostly ignored him.
Wrote him off
as just a nuisance.
That's all.
Remember this:
"Whatever happens, you
have to stick to your guns."
That's Phyllo's message to you.
Right, as if I need it.
[PI]
Master Yata,
I've found the
unidentified phenomena.
[YATA]
Where's Kuhn?
I believe he's
in the main room.
[YATA]
Destroy the target.
If possible, get a sample.
Yes.
So what's up?
Something new happening?
It's Haseo,
he's back again.
Yeah, I know.
Don't you wanna go see him?
Why would I?
Whaddaya mean, why?
I guess I can understand.
Well, if he logged in,
that means he's fine,
doesn't it?
Maintain a moderate distance.
That's one of my principles.
[TOHTA] Oh, so you're
a spectator by nature?
I don't wanna get burned
by getting involved with others.
That depends on who
those others might be.
[SABURO] You have a history
of getting involved
with the wrong people
and finding yourself
in sticky situations, right?
Well, I won't deny it.
Y'know, Haseo's
kinda like Chinese food.
What?
You get full just by
smelling its enticing aroma.
It's kinda like that.
But it makes you hungry,
and you won't get sick of,
well, looking at it.
So you're fine with
just smelling and looking?
Yeah.
It's way more fun.
Are you in the bathroom?
As long as there's
someone like you around,
I'm pretty sure I don't
have to worry about anything.
[SABURO]
Are you gonna quit again?
This game is only
one aspect of real life.
I have all these other things
I have to take care of.
I dunno what you're up to,
but I'm sure you'll
be fine, Tawaraya.
Leave things here to me,
and go do whatever
it is you need to do.
[TOHTA]
Uh-huh. That's my plan.
Danke Schön!
First you call up the Avatar,
and then you proceed
with your attack.
If you don't think
you can handle it,
withdraw your Avatar,
and I'll do it myself.
I've done this before, okay?
I know what I'm doing!
Whoa!
[KUHN]
What is this?
Let's go.
Wait a second!
[PI] There's something
inside the bug hole.
What are your orders,
Master Yata?
[YATA] I'd like to see
what comes out of it.
[YATA] It's imitating
an active life form?
[PI]
Master Yata!
Your orders?!
[YATA]
That's enough.
Destroy it!
Yes!
Don't chicken out now!
Let's go!
All right!
I really can't believe
you're dead, Phyllo.
I just can't accept
that you're gone.
Why now?
Forget about
getting a sample--
that thing was a beast.
For now,
let's just go back.
Yeah, for sure.
If that kind of thing
starts popping up
all over the game,
this world will be destroyed.
[MAN]
Are you the Haseo
that's being talked
about in the forums?
[MAN]
I've been through a lot, too.
I have a feeling I could
become friends with you.
Get lost.
I see.
Well.
I am the Silver Knight.
You and I have a lot
in common, you know.
Maybe we'll meet again sometime.
I'm not interested.
[TOHTA]
That's the story.
So you guys just
keep playing the game
like you have been.
[PILOCCHIO] We started
an information service!
Are you serious?
[ITA]
That's right,
we decided to
expand our business!
[PILOCCHIO] We figured
we'd be better off
than dealing with items.
You know what--
[PILOCCHIO] So don't worry,
you go abroad and study!
[ITA] Come back any time
if you're lonely.
Nevermind that.
[TABBY]
There he is!
Hey, Tohta!
Hi! What's going on, Tabby?
[TABBY]
I'm sorry.
For what?
I feel kinda bad that
I disbanded the guild
that you helped me start.
[TOHTA]
Oh, that doesn't matter.
It seems like you've
settled down a bit now.
Mmm-hmm.
And about these,
I won't need them anymore.
Are you quitting?
[TABBY] I have a goal
in real life now.
As much as I'd like to take
them off your hands, Tabby,
the fact is, I'm quitting too.
[TABBY]
Meow?
Like you, I've
also got my real life.
Would you like us
to take them for you?
[TABBY]
Huh?
'Cause we'll always be here
if you want them back.
I'm sorry, but they're
not really for sale.
Don't worry, you can
trust them. It's safe.
They won't sell these.
[TABBY]
Really?
Here, yeah.
If I can achieve my goal,
then I'll come back
and get them.
Thanks! Come again!
That's my line...
This is it.
I guess I'm alone, then.
Any regrets?
Yeah, but you
can't turn back time.
Well, I can imagine
after all that,
you wouldn't have any
energy left, would you?
That's not it.
Haseo, are you lonely
being by yourself?
Just look around
and you'll see a lot
of people are that way.
I mean, you only
have to look at me!
[HASEO]
You, too?
You know,
before there was TV,
people used to
watch the fireplace
or gaze at candles.
Where do you get
this crap from, anyway?
[SABURO]
Human beings just require
plenty of visual stimulation
from things that have movement.
[HASEO]
What?
[SABURO]
Don't you get it?
[HASEO]
No, I don't.
[SABURO] There's someone
who's watching you
and who cares about you.
So why don't you go and
make your move, already?
What was that for?
[SABURO laughs]
You should know...
...I'm always on the move.
Hey, how would you like
to heal PCs with me?
[PC 26C]
Huh?
[SEISAKU]
In a game like this,
people need to be healed,
don't you think?
You should--
C'mon, quit messing around!
[SEISAKU]
W-Wait!
--[SEISAKU] But she's hot!
--[HIDEYO] I can't believe you!
[SEISAKU] Wait!
C'mon man, she's a babe!
Look at her! She's smokin'...
Loser.
[TABBY]
Haseo?
Haseo! Haseo!
Haseo!
Welcome back!
[HASEO]
Hey, get off me!
But I'm so happy
you're back!
[HASEO]
You're getting on my nerves.
[TABBY]
It's you!
It really is you!
It's totally you!
Haseo!
[HASEO]
Hey, get off me!
[TABBY]
You're lying.
I wouldn't lie about that.
I'm sorry.
But why?
Why wouldn't he tell me,
of all people?
We were so close
and we always talked a lot.
Yeah, well,
it's not exactly
small talk or anything.
Phyllo. It's just like him.
You know what?
Oh, nevermind.
[HASEO]
I'm going.
Where to?
[HASEO]
I don't know. Wherever.
But I can't stand still.
Are you...
...gonna kill PKs again?
Don't worry.
There's absolutely no use
in doing the same thing twice.
[TABBY]
I see.
Are you gonna keep
playing the game
even though you're back
to where you started?
[HASEO]
Well, to be honest,
I can't think of any
other way to go on.
[TABBY]
Haseo.
[HASEO]
Uh-huh?
[TABBY]
Listen to me.
You're the one, Haseo.
The only one
who can save Shino.
No, not on my own.
You're right.
Listen.
I've been thinking
of becoming a nurse!
[HASEO]
That's great.
The way I see it is...
...I'd be much better off
helping Shino in the real world.
That's gonna
take years, y'know?
[TABBY]
Oh yeah, you're right.
Well until then,
I guess I'll be
the one saving her.
[TABBY]
But if you can't do it...
Whatever!
That's why you can't be messing
around by yourself anymore.
Look, if you
can't do it, I will.
What're you tryin'
to say? I'm weak?
I like you, Haseo.
I've decided.
I'm gonna do my best for my
sake and study really hard.
That's why...
That's why you need to do
your best for your sake!
[HASEO]
Yeah.
Of course.
The time has finally come.
What do you mean?
As the Raven guild,
as a group of players
who possess the Factor,
let's make contact with Haseo.
You can leave it to me.
[YATA] And we'll need
a name for these.
[KUHN]
A name?
[YATA] The characteristics
will be defined by the name.
So we must be careful
of what we label it.
Of course.
[YATA]
A.I.
[PI]
Artificial Intelligence.
[YATA] It seems the
unidentified phenomenon
is the outcome of an
uncontrolled and abnormal A.I.
that originated from
the realms of the Net.
Therefore, we'll
refer to it as AIDA,
an Artificial
Intelligence Data Anomaly.
[PI]
AIDA?
[OVAN]
Become stronger, Haseo.
Strong enough to kill me.
And if you can't
get stronger than that,
it will...
Something completely unique
that only you possess.
[HASEO]
I don't get it.
It's amazing!
Today's youth seem to lack
manners and morality.
Read the manual!
So tell me, are you?
I'll read it later.
I know it's hard,
but don't quit.
I don't know you,
but I don't wanna
go on with this game.
It's so stupid and pointless.
It's not stupid.
And it's not pointless.
Welcome, Haseo.
Welcome to The World.
I have absolutely no idea
what you're talking about.
There would be
nothing left to enjoy
if we knew everything.
I'm so sorry.
[HASEO]
Huh?
It's just...
...I have to stay strong.
Know what, Shino?
You are staying strong.
I'm not like her.
Aura lost hope for this world
and decided that
she had to run away.
[SHINO]
You know what?
The wonderful thing
about this place
is that it allows you
to think and feel calm.
I feel as though I'm at the
beginning of something.
Of knowing what I need to do.
This is where I
decided to change
my Player Character's color.
This is where Ovan and I decided
to search for the
Key of the Twilight.
And this is the place where
I first heard of you, Haseo.
This is where I always came
when I was about
to begin something new.
Now...
...it's clear!