[CHIKA]
Lookin' good, girl!
You know that you've
got our votes
when the election comes around.
Sweet!
[HIKARI]
I'm Hikari Sakurada.
At first glance, you'd
think I was a normal,
super cute elementary
school student.
And you'd totally
be right about that!
But I'm also royalty!
And I'm in the
running to be king!
Aoi's still in the
number one spot.
At least, that's what
the polls are saying.
I saw that too.
And Akane's rocking
a close second.
[BOTH gasp]
Wait. What ranking are you?
Fifth!
I'm less popular than
Shiori. So embarrassing.
[CROWD cheering]
[laughing]
[HIKARI] The crown is gonna
go to the most beautiful
and popular contender.
Which means...
I'll be king for sure!
[AKANE screaming]
Why am I in charge
of groceries again?!
The world's against me.
Be sure to get curry
while you're out!
I'd rather take a
nuclear bomb to the face.
Well, that's harsh!
Do you really hate
curry that much?
You're totally missing
the point here.
I don't want the public eye
following my every move.
I still don't get why
you're so hung up on that.
The whole country has seen
the shots of your panties.
Make her stop!
Enough with the shouting.
Shouldn't you be focused
on campaigning?
Wait, we have to do that?
I'm working on it, okay?
Neither of you will beat me,
so don't even bother.
[TERU, AKANE gasp]
[AKANE]
Try not to let her get to you.
After all, you've been
working hard, right?
No, I've been slacking off.
[AKANE] How do you expect to
win if you don't at least try?
Oh, It'll be fine!
I can snag an easy
win out of this thing.
My power will take care of that!
A little grown-up charm,
and they'll be smitten!
All I need to do is add a little
bit of bounce here or there,
and the entire nation will
be eating out of my hand.
Until you go back to
an A-cup the next day.
[KANADE]
First off, what's the point?
Everyone in the country knows
you're only ten years old.
Second, you'd be changing your
appearance, not your age.
And trying to win by your looks
alone is shallow at best.
I might listen to you
if you weren't in love
with that mirror!
Whatever.
My boobs are still growing, and
you're as big as you'll ever be.
[KANADE] The shape matters
more than the size, kid.
No, bigger is better!
Shu said so!
Take that back!
--All you need is a handful!
--You agree with me, don't you?
Poor Akane.
[AKANE]
Hey, don't pity me.
I'm sorry.
[AKANE]
Please stop.
I'm bound to win.
Especially since Akane and Aoi
don't care about the election.
You don't know that.
[KANADE] If she gets serious,
I don't stand a chance.
[AKANE]
She's already ranked first.
Doesn't that mean
it's game over?
[KANADE]
No, not necessarily.
I don't know why,
but Aoi doesn't seem
interested in the throne.
I wouldn't be surprised
if she took steps
to lower her popularity.
You think she'd do
bad stuff? Like what?
I don't know.
Like eating the pudding you were
saving without your permission?
[AKANE] That was you,
wasn't it, you sneak?
Don't you have
groceries to go buy?
Tell you what,
I'll tag along too!
[HIKARI]
Sweet! A camera!
Time to appeal to my
soon-to-be subjects.
[AKANE]
Wait, Hikari.
Not that way. There's too
much surveillance.
Yeah, but--
[AKANE] Take one more
step in that direction
and it'll be your last.
[HIKARI]
I think she means it.
Listen to me, Hikari.
I know you really
wanna be popular,
but it won't happen if you
keep forcing it. Understand?
This is politics...
[HIKARI]
Why'd I even come with her?
If you become king,
you'll have all kinds
of responsibilities.
The well-being of the people
will always come
before your own.
You'll have to spend
every waking moment
thinking of ways to
improve the country
and its relationship with
the rest of the world.
It takes work. And a
whole lot of patience.
Not to mention major diplomacy
skills. And leadership.
Do you get what I'm saying? Uh.
Um. Hikari?
Pretty kitty!
[HIKARI]
Wait for me!
[AKANE]
She's gone. What should I do?
I can't go shopping
without someone
to talk to people for me!
Why would you leave me, Hikari?
I guess I have no choice.
[AKANE]
Um... Excuse me, sir?
[stammering]
Could you please help me
find my little sister?
[MAN whimpers]
Come out, kitty!
[HIKARI]
Do you need help getting down?
Hey, I know!
If I mature myself,
I'll be taller, and presto!
Now we're talking!
Come here, kitty,
you're safe now.
Geez! I don't
look that different!
Hikari!
[HIKARI]
You're gonna be okay.
[AKANE] There you are!
I was looking everywhere.
Now, let's get going.
Sorry! Wrong person!
It's me, dummy!
Stop playing around.
Hurry. If we wait any longer
there might be a crowd.
I couldn't hurry
even if I wanted to.
I'm having a little issue.
[screams]
[AKANE]
Here.
This should do until
we get back home.
There's no way this'll work!
We're home.
It's about time.
Uh. Do I know you?
--Who are they?
--I'm not sure.
[MISAKI]
OMG!
Akane, I could just
gobble you up!
[AKANE]
You're squeezing too tight, Sis!
[MISAKI]
You're totes adorbz!
[KANADE]
What did you do? Shrink Akane?
Yeah. I needed to switch
clothes for a little bit.
But isn't she a
little too small?
I may have overdone it.
I hope she's ready for a day
of being Misaki's plaything.
If she's lucky, she won't
lose her sanity.
Anyway, I'm glad you
guys finished your errand
and made it home in one piece.
[HIKARI]
Uhh.
[SHU] So... where are
all of the groceries?
[HIKARI screams]
[NEWSCASTER B]
It looks like it's shaping up
to be another thrilling day!
[NEWSCASTER A] Yep! And to
make it even more exciting,
we'll now announce
the public opinion poll
for the first week of June!
[NEWSCASTER B]
Ready? I know I am!
[HIKARI]
Huh?
I rescued a helpless kitty cat
and I didn't rank up at all?
What gives?
It's probably because there
weren't any cameras around.
[HIKARI gasps]
You're such an airhead, Hikari.
Don't let it get you down, okay?
Remember, there's
always next time.
Just keep working at it.
You're right. Next time.
No way!
This cannot be happening!
That's three times in a row.
Why is life out to get me?
Maybe 'cause you
keep hiding from it?
How come I don't get to draw?
If I don't do chores,
I'll never become a man!
Worry about that when
you're a little older, Teru.
[SHIORI]
Hello. I'm Shiori Sakurada.
I'm the youngest
of the royal family.
[TERU groaning]
[SHIORI]
Are you okay, Teru?
[TERU]
Oh, no you don't!
Calm down, Jackal. I mean it.
[SHIORI] Sometimes I don't
really understand my brother.
I think it's because
he's a year older.
[TERU]
Leave it to me, Akane!
I'll tackle the
shopping for you!
You're pretty gung-ho
about chores.
What lit this fire
under your butt?
I wanna be able to protect
all of you someday,
but that is never gonna happen
unless I can get stronger.
I need to find every challenge
I can and beat them one by one!
Epic, bro! I'm with
you. All the way!
Big Brother! I'll
get the groceries...
[SHIORI]
Teru can be pretty careless.
I'm afraid he'll get in trouble
if he goes shopping
all by himself.
I'm going with you.
But, Shiori, this is
a trial of courage.
There's no telling what dangers
we'll face along the way.
[SHIORI]
I have to do this.
I'm going.
I get it, you must've been
feeling left out, too.
All right. But don't leave my
side for a second, understand?
[SHIORI]
Mh-hm.
Rock on! Let's do this.
[SHU]
Be safe out there.
[AKANE]
I'm such a horrible person!
I made them go off
all on their own!
You could still tag along.
Yeah, but they seemed
so excited about it.
That's it! Hikari,
I need you for a sec.
This is bad! I forgot to
grab the shopping bag!
We barely left and we've
already hit a brick wall.
I can't quit! Everyone at
home is counting on me!
We're going back, Shiori!
When did you?
On we go!
[barking]
Hey! Keep it down, you mutt!
If you don't...
[SHIORI] Please, Mr. Dog,
we just wanna pass by,
if that's okay.
We're not bad people.
[DOG A]
Oh, is that so?
In that case, I'm sorry.
I thought you were invaders
after my stash of old socks.
[SHIORI] I can talk to
any animal or object
with my thoughts.
[DOG A]
You may pass.
Yeah! You better bow!
[SHIORI]
Thank you, sir.
[TERU]
Let's go, Shiori!
Phew!
If we didn't have the king's
spirit we may not have survived.
Curse that demon!
If only I could
use my Limit Over!
Then the fight would've been
done in three seconds flat!
I'd have made that
flea bag eat his own tail!
[SHIORI]
Whenever Teru uses his power,
he has more strength than
any adult could dream of.
[TERU] Still, I can't go around
using my gift carelessly.
"With great power comes
great responsibility."
That's what mom told me
when she had me make
this contract with her.
[SHIORI] She did that
'cause you're a klutz.
[AKANE]
I said I wanted to be 27.
Why'd you turn me
into a rug rat again?
You totally said seven.
Besides, I rock the grown up...
What's the matter, Shiori?
Huh? Hey, who are you?
[BOTH]
We've been spotted!
Answer me! Why are you
sneaking around?
Are you following us?
Are you agents of darkness?
[HIKARI]
Shiori knows it's us.
[HIKARI] We're just two normal
gals out for a normal walk.
[AKANE] Maybe you should get
back to that errand of yours.
I forgot.
I have an important mission
I need to complete!
I thought that truck
had our number.
Now that we've made
it across the street,
the real challenge begins.
Uh-oh.
Big Brother, I can't
find the shopping list.
Those two girls.
They must've stolen it somehow!
[SHIORI] Oh. Where are you,
Miss Grocery List?
We can't do this without you.
[SHOPPING LIST] Over here!
I've been here the whole time.
[TERU]
They're counting on us!
We're gonna be heroes
when we get home.
[TERU gasps]
[SHIORI]
Here we go.
Mr. Dog, may we pass, please?
[DOG B]
I smell it.
Hand over the grub
and you won't get hurt.
[SHIORI] I'm sorry,
but I can't do that.
[DOG B]
Fine then! You asked for it!
[TERU]
You coward.
How dare you attack someone
who can't defend themselves!
I promised my mother I wouldn't
use my power irresponsibly,
but--
If you ever threaten
someone I care about again,
I won't hesitate to
kick your teeth in!
[DOG B whining]
Shiori. How're ya
doing? You okay?
Yeah.
Awesome!
Y'know, you're one
tough toddler, Sis.
Come on. Let's get home so
we can get some food!
Hm?
[TERU] I can't take my eyes
off you for a second, can I?
Is the bag too heavy
for you? I can carry it.
[SHIORI]
Nah, I've got it.
[HIKARI]
I need ideas.
There's gotta be a fast way
to get popular, right?
Earth to Princess Hikari.
If you're going to space out,
could you not do it on my bed?
[HIKARI]
Nah, I'm good here. Thanks.
[TV AUDIENCE screaming]
Look! They're broadcasting
Sacchy's concert!
[HIKARI]
Who, what?
Hello!
I'm so humbled that you all
came out to see me! Thank you!
It's her first live show
but there are over ten
thousand people there!
Uh, Hikari? You still with us?
[HIKARI]
Bingo!
This is amazing.
Who knew it was so easy
to become popular?
Hey, Borscht, you in here?
There's my pretty boy.
You ready for dinner?
Whatever it is you're planning,
don't go overboard.
Consider that your only warning.
I don't want them to copy me.
So, until I'm actually an idol,
this will be my little secret.
I have to audition first?
And elementary school students
need a guardian with them.
Well, that's a bummer.
If I was two years older,
I could go all by myself.
Geez.
The rest of the world really
needs to catch up with me.
[gasps]
Why wait when I can transform
into a middle school student?
I'm a genius!
But If I want to pull this off,
I need to find some
bigger clothes.
Akane's lacking in the chest.
Kanade would kill me.
I guess Misaki is the winner.
Hm. None of these
have a "wow" factor.
Doesn't she have any
interesting clothes?
[HARUKA clearing throat]
Would you like it if someone
started digging through
all your stuff
without permission?
No, not really.
But I don't have anything
to wear for my audition.
Say what now?
I really want to
become the next king,
so I tried to think of a way
to get popular quickly.
I decided being an idol
was my best shot.
What for?
It sounded like fun!
So, what do you think?
You might be onto something.
I can keep your secret.
And I'll help out.
You really mean it?
Just this once, okay?
Understood!
[HARUKA] But, if you're going
to do it, do it with gusto!
[HIKARI]
Maybe this was a bad idea.
[HARUKA]
With her brother's help,
Hikari passed the first audition
and kept everyone at home
completely in the dark.
Looking back on it, there were
easier ways to meet her goal.
And they may have gotten
a little carried away.
But why do it if you're
going to take the easy out?
That's lazy. The harder the
work, the sweeter the victory.
[HARUKA]
They've come far.
And now their destiny is
well within their grasp.
Remember the blood, sweat,
and tears that got us here.
Yeah.
If they knew the truth, they'd
probably treat you differently.
For now, it's best to keep
your lineage a secret.
Your friend deserves
our gratitude.
If you weren't using
her name, we'd be screwed.
You can pay me back once
you're a big shot idol.
Thank you, Chika.
[HARUKA] Show them
your overwhelming charm.
Make yourself indispensable.
So when they do find
out who you are,
you'll be too popular for them
to let go. You'll be an idol.
Make me proud.
Yeah. You got it.
I'm here for the second round.
That's great!
I just need to see your ID
and you'll be all set to go.
Oh. My ID?
We also accept
school identification.
[HIKARI]
Awesome!
Here you go!
Thank you.
Huh? Hold on,
this can't be right.
[HIKARI] Oh, crap! I gave
her my actual school card!
So, uh. We made a mistake.
[HIKARI]
Wait. Does she not recognize me?
According to this, you're
in elementary school.
Someone on staff must've
thought you were older
when they screened your photos.
I'm very sorry, but
we're not recruiting
elementary school
students at this time.
Be sure to check the age
limits in the future!
[HIKARI]
Uhh...
[HARUKA]
Huh?
[HIKARI]
Well, I feel dumb.
Showing my ID never
even crossed my mind.
[HARUKA] This wouldn't
have been a problem
if I had disguised myself
as her guardian.
All she had to do was use
her power on me as well.
I'll tell her that later.
[HARUKA]
Let's go home.
[HIKARI]
Yeah.
[HARUKA] And so, our
heroes left. Defeated.
Nature calls. Would
you mind waiting?
Sure. Got nothing
better to do.
[HIKARI sighs]
I'm not very lucky.
[MATSUOKA] Excuse me, Miss.
Do you have a moment?
[HIKARI]
Huh?
I'm a recruiter for a big
local entertainment business.
Would you like to be an idol--?
[HIKARI]
Yes, please!
[MATSUOKA chuckles]
You've got a lot
of spirit. I like that.
[MATSUOKA] She has a sense
of refinement about her.
She might be exactly
what we're looking for.
Our organization's main
office and training building
is right around the corner.
When do you have some
free time to check it out?
Now!
[HARUKA]
Where'd she go?
[PRESIDENT] Well done, Matsuoka.
You found us an amazing girl.
I'm actually kinda surprised
that no one had
scouted her before.
Morning, everyone.
[HIKARI]
Uh.
Hey, you're Sacchy!
You're the reason I'm here!
'Scuse me?
Your concert inspired me!
[SACCHY] I feel like I've seen
her somewhere before.
Awesome! I can't wait to tell
Chika I met you in person!
Well, then, what do you think?
You serious about
becoming an idol?
Yeah! More than anything!
That's great!
But first I need to talk to
your parents to make sure
there are no issues.
Would it be okay if I
tried calling them now?
[HIKARI]
Uh, sure! Just one sec!
[HARUKA] Darn it, Hikari.
You better be okay.
[PHONE RINGER]
Big smelly Haru's calling!
What's her phone
doing in my bag?
Oh, that's right.
I left my phone in Haru's bag
so it wouldn't be a distraction.
Come to think of it,
I left Haru too.
We could always use our landline
to get in touch
with them at home.
If you give me your phone number
I can take care of it myself.
Actually...
...I don't know the
number at home by heart.
[PRESIDENT chuckles]
In that case,
would it be alright with you if
we paid them a visit in person?
[HIKARI]
Yeah, that's fine!
You wanna tag along, Sacchy?
I'd like to, but I'm
recording in a minute.
If she isn't dead,
I'm gonna kill her!
There you are!
[HIKARI]
Hm?
I was worried sick!
Just what have you been doing?
Getting scouted! These
guys wanna make me an idol!
Who? These two?
You know better than to
run off with strangers.
Second Prince Haruka.
[PRESIDENT A]
Oh...
Uh, Miss Hikari, what was
your last name again?
[chuckles] I didn't
mention it before?
[MATSUOKA]
Your Majesty!
I didn't realize who
your daughter was.
In my ignorance, I treated
her with great disrespect!
For that, I beg you
for your forgiveness!
However, I don't think
this was a coincidence.
You see, Princess Hikari
has an innate talent
that every idol dreams about!
Please, sire! Let us
represent your daughter!
It would be our
most humble honor!
That sounds good to me.
Thanks, Daddy!
I knew you'd understand!
You're the best!
[HIKARI] Hey, hey!
How's it going everyone?
I'm the band new idol,
Laito Sakurapa!
I'm excited to be here!
And I'm working really hard
to make my debut amazing!
So you're still disguising
yourself as a middle schooler
and keeping your
identity secret.
Uh-huh. At least for now.
And you're okay with that?
I've heard of lying about
your age to be younger,
but never really
the other way around.
I'd love to wear
clothes like that.
[SHU] You could always
become an idol.
[AKANE]
No thanks.
I have a question, Hikari.
The whole point of this was
to raise your popularity
for the election, right?
[HIKARI]
You got it!
[HARUKA] Then why are
you hiding your identity?
[HIKARI]
Uh!
[HIKARI] Daughter number
five at your service!
[SATSUKI] Hikari can act
a little spoiled at times,
but she's full of life,
positive energy, and honesty.
She's also quite
popular at school.
If she became king,
I'm sure our country
would transform
into a fun and lively place.
Is there anything that
you'd like to say, sweetie?
[HIKARI] I'll make this nation
a place of fun and fashion!
Just so you know,
my favorite ruler from
history is Maria Theresa!
I'll be patiently waiting
for your honest vote!
Until next time!