[AKANE]
The summer flew by.
Now the election's
only six months away.
[AKANE]
Aoi, I'm going to be king.
Once I have the crown,
I'll live a quiet life.
[AKANE]
I made up my mind to go for it.
but I haven't really done much
in the way of campaigning
for the crown since then.
[HARUKA]
It's considered entertainment,
so it's perfectly legal.
But I know how
embarrassed you get.
[AKANE] It's time for
me to make a change.
[AKANE]
Hello, everyone.
First, let me apologize
for the disruption.
My name's Akane... Sakurada.
It's nice to... meet you.
I'm not all that great at
speaking in front of people,
but I will be a great king.
So, I hope you'll consider...
giving me your vote.
Akane Sa--
[FAN CLUB]
Vote for Akane!
[AKANE screeches]
[NEWSCASTER B] Despite
stammering through her speech,
Princess Akane left a good
impression on the citizens
who call her innocence
a "breath of fresh air..."
[HIKARI]
Look at that!
Whoa.
How did you ever
survive speaking
in front of all those people?
[AKANE]
I don't know!
You're campaigning?
Seems kinda weird
since even the pictures on
your fan page freak you out.
I won't give in!
When I become king, I'm gonna
regulate the internet so hard!
I'm not sure you can do that.
[TERU] Check it out
I'm so gonna win with these!
[AKANE]
"Annihilating evil at its core
and guiding the
world to the end"?
Um, what does that
even mean, Teru?
That last part actually
sounds kinda terrifying.
What? I thought it
sounded pretty epic.
You guys really don't like it?
I think it sounds kinda awesome.
Speaking of awesomeness,
I get to be police
chief for a day.
You mean, "Laito" does.
I've got a ton of campaign
events to attend this week.
Really?
[TERU] All right! Time to hang
these all over the city!
[SHIORI]
I'm coming with you.
[SHU]
Hey, Akane.
If you want, I can accompany
you this weekend.
[AKANE] Yes, please!
That'd be great, Shu!
Everyone else is campaigning
for the crown like crazy.
Meanwhile, we're just sitting
here twiddling our thumbs.
We've been helping
out at school.
But then again, that's
all we've been doing.
I think we need some
excitement in our lives.
We should be idols like Hikari.
I'm in! We'd totally
rock as idols, y'know?
Sounds like too much work.
Whatever, it's not like we have
a chance of winning anyway.
Hey, is there any more pudding?
Haruka! Why aren't
you being more helpful?
Like I could get a
word in. Good grief.
I don't get why I was even
invited to the "Misaki Summit"
in the first place.
What's the topic of
this discussion anyway?
Um. Election strategy.
[HARUKA]
Wow. You're in it to win it.
Well, duh! I can't let the
other princesses beat me!
Look at Akane!
She only wants to win
so she can get rid of
the surveillance cameras
and save herself from
more embarrassment!
Then there's Hikari,
who just wants the whole
kingdom to fawn over her.
That's why she became an idol!
Aoi couldn't care less
about the election,
but she's still in the lead
without even trying!
And Kanade's totally
up to something
even though I have no
freakin' idea what it is!
[PLAYER A]
You're in the clear, go!
[PLAYER B]
I'm open! Over here!
Go on, shoot it!
[PLAYER B]
Follow it up, let's move!
[PLAYER C]
Open net! Go, go!
[PLAYER A]
He takes it up and--
[KANADE]
Akane!
You wanna come play outside
with your big sister?
[AKANE]
Yeah!
[SHU]
You're not allowed.
Mom told us we're supposed
to stay in the house.
You'll just have to come with
us and make sure we stay safe.
I don't think you know
what "stay at home" means.
[KANADE]
You're not the boss of me!
Only Mom and Dad can
tell me what to do!
Nope, I am the boss
of you 'cause I'm older.
You were only born 30
minutes before me, dummy!
I'm still older than you,
it doesn't matter by how much.
Well that doesn't make
you smarter than me!
If you're not gonna come,
then we'll go and
have fun on our own!
[sighs]
Okay, fine, you made
your point, Kanade.
[AKANE laughing]
[AKANE]
Yay! Do it again!
C'mon! We should
go back home now.
No way, we wanna play
a little longer!
[SHU] If we're not home before
mom, she's gonna be mad.
We're coming!
[KANADE]
Wait just a sec.
I've got something
cool to show you!
What is it?
Watch!
[SHU]
C'mon, Kana!
Ta-da!
A Rose Typhoon costume for me?
If you keep making stuff
whenever you want.
You're gonna run outta
New Year's money.
All that magic stuff comes out
of your savings, y'know!
I can't wait to go home
and show it to mommy!
Uh! No, you can't go yet!
I still have another cool
thing to make for you!
[AKANE gasps]
You made a castle for me?
Yeah. Pretty cool, huh?
Can Rose Typhoon go inside?
Yeah, of course you can.
I dunno how to get
all the way up there.
What?
Uh-oh, there's supposed
to be a staircase.
See? Told you you'd
run out of savings.
[KANADE growls]
[AKANE]
But I wanna go inside.
Okay, I tell you what.
I can teleport you up there
but just this one time.
[AKANE]
You can?
[SHU]
Yeah, just take my hand.
[KANADE] No, wait! I can finish
the stairs. I know I can!
[SHU] But there's nothing
left in your bank account.
[KANADE]
It'll be fine!
Oh, wow!
Whoa, she did it. Uh. Oh no.
[SHU]
Akane!
[KANADE]
What... what happened?
[gasps]
[KANADE]
No!
That day changed Shu's life.
He lost partial use of his legs.
He could still walk but
running is too much for him.
[SHU] When I grow up,
I'll be a soccer sensation!
[KANADE] That was all
he ever dreamed about.
And I took that dream
away from him.
Unfortunately, I can't
heal him with my powers.
But maybe I can when I'm king.
I'll spare no expense
on medical research.
I wanna bring Shu's smile back.
I swear that I will someday.
[AKANE] Someone's gotta
be rigging the chore cup!
Please tell me why I keep
ending up with this?
[SHU]
Hey, whoa.
It's not our fault you
keep picking that one.
[AKANE wailing]
She's bawling.
I almost feel bad.
[AKANE]
I get it!
This is merely another trial
on the path to kingship,
and I'll overcome!
I shall venture forth.
Into treacherous lands.
Where people and cars
converge in a deadly dance!
From there into the shadow
fortress of the supermarket!
And bring back dinner.
Wish me well!
[SHU]
She's still got a ways to go,
but at least she's
trying, right?
But you're not really
trying, are you, Shu?
For what?
To be king and stuff.
[SHU]
Nah, I guess not.
I can't think of much
reason to be king.
Not over any of you.
[MISAKI]
Hm?
For real?
[SHU]
Yeah.
[HARUKA] It's nice of you to
help the team out on a Sunday.
They're a good group,
and they really needed
to snag a win this weekend.
That all it was?
[HIKARI] Hello, everyone!
My name is Laito Sakurapa!
I'm your honorary
police chief for the day
and I'm proud to work
with all of you!
Let's keep the streets safe!
It's Hikari.
She's starting to take
this thing seriously.
[TERU]
I want to, well, uh--
[SHIORI] Make use of
the awesome power I have.
Uh. Make use of the
awesome power I have.
[SHIORI]
If I'm elected,
I will give my all to protecting
this great kingdom.
If I'm elected,
I will give my all to protecting
this great kingdom.
I can't pick out which
one's making the speech.
[ANNOUNCER C]
Here she is,
please welcome to the
stage our special guest.
This spring, Princess
Kanade will serve
as special advisor to
our Sports Foundation.
She'll help us teach
the kingdom's youth
to make healthy
lifestyle choices.
Wow. Kanade isn't messing
around with her campaigning.
She really wants this.
[YUNIKO]
Ugh!
Everyone else is campaigning
for the crown like crazy.
Meanwhile, we're just sitting
here twiddling our thumbs.
I'm pretty sure we've had
this conversation before.
Yeah, most definitely.
But seriously, we should
become idols, too.
Why's everyone getting
bent up over it now,
it's not like our chances
have gotten better.
This isn't about
who's gonna win.
It's that everybody
seems to be so focused
on campaigning for themselves.
They're ignoring the
people's needs, y'know?
And that just seems wrong to me.
That's easy to say when
you're doing nothing.
[MISAKI wails]
Yeah, like you can talk, Bro.
[HARUKA]
I didn't mean like that!
Oh, I see, you've turned
traitor and sided against me.
But that's not what I said.
I mean, sure, you have
to put the people first.
But it takes a whole lot more
than that to be a good leader,
Misaki.
It's not as though our
sisters aren't thinking
about the people,
of course they are.
They're just doing the best they
can with the skills they have.
In the end, it's up to
the citizens to decide.
All you can do is tell
them where you stand
and hope for the best.
Listen here!
The monarch's actual job
is to govern this kingdom!
Obviously, the best
person for the throne
is the one who's willing to put
this nation above anything!
[HARUKA] And do you think
you're the one to do that?
I can!
[REVI]
I'm not so sure about that.
[MISAKI gasps]
[HARUKA] Wow, you can't
even agree with yourself.
[REVI] Be honest, why're
you getting all worked up?
It's not about your sisters
gunning for the crown, is it?
No, you're upset because
Haruka stood up for them.
You're not "fighting
for justice."
You're jealous of them.
[RAIO] You can't hide
your feelings from us.
The only reason you want the
crown is to impress Haruka.
[gasps]
[HARUKA]
What's that look for?
Are you all right?
She's realized she wants to be
king for selfish reasons, too.
I doubt she'll go around bad
mouthing all her sisters anymore
after a major
revelation like this.
[MISAKI]
I'm just as bad as they are.
No. I'm even worse for
being a gigantic hypocrite.
Hey, Misaki.
You know, I really think
you'd make a good king.
No matter what
the reason may be.
[MISAKI gasps]
You honestly care about people.
You always put others
before yourself.
I wish I was more like you.
If you want to be king,
I think you should go for it.
Because you'd make
an awesome one.
Then I will.
I didn't think I had
it in me before now,
but I'll campaign
and try my best.
Would you mind helping me?
[gasps]
Well, sure, I don't see why not?
I'm in. But if we're gonna
do this, we do it right.
[MISAKI, CLONES]
Yeah!
[YUNIKO]
Whoa!
I've never seen Bubu this
fired up about anything.
[HARUKA]
We were changing.
At first, it was
just tiny steps,
but slowly they grew to
strides, leaps, and bounds.
Things we once thought
impossible became the everyday.
I think maybe that's
why Father decided
to hold this election now,
while we're young.
He's giving us the chance
to find our weaknesses
and overcome them before we have
to make our own in the world.
[BUBU] I hear the sound
of pudding approaching.
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA]
You hear pudding?!
[SHU]
Huh? What was that?
[PRINCIPAL]
We have a special visitor today.
This is Princess Kanade
of the royal family.
It's nice to meet you all.
I've been working hard
to become king,
but today, I'm here just
to have fun with you.
She's even prettier
in real life!
[KIDS laughing]
[KANADE]
You're very good.
Is that a drawing of your mommy?
[KAE]
Nuh-uh! It's Princess Aoi!
She's cool! I'm gonna give
her my vote for sure!
[TEACHER] That's enough
drawing for now, Kae.
Why don't we go sing a song?
[KAE] But, Teacher,
I'm not done drawing yet!
But doesn't singing
sound like a lot of fun?
[KAE]
I guess so.
[TEACHER]
Come along over here.
Bye, bye!
[KANADE] Even little
kids are taken with her.
My biggest rival for the
crown is definitely Aoi.
[groans]
I am so done.
Hey. Are you alive?
[KANADE]
What happened to her?
[AOI]
She's just a little tuckered out
from all the campaigning.
I don't blame her. She's been
going full speed for days.
[KANADE] Wait, have you
guys been helping her out
this entire time?
Yep.
I've been hauling materials
for her all weekend.
I hope she does well when it's
time for the votes to come in.
She's been campaigning hard.
Who's there?
[KANADE]
It's me. Can I come in?
Kanade? Yeah, sure.
Okay, now be honest with me, do
you want to become king or not?
Whoa, where did
this come from?
[KANADE]
If you're not in it to win,
then you should dedicate
yourself to Akane's campaign.
You can help her
overcome her shyness.
Plus, you won't have to be king,
it's a win-win, y'know?
[AOI]
Let's make one thing clear,
I'm not helping her just
so I can avoid the crown.
You make it sound as though I'm
using her. It's not like that.
I know. Why don't
you talk to daddy?
Tell him you want
out of the election.
Father, please,
you must understand that I don't
want to rule the kingdom.
'Kay! Love ya, sweetie.
Better yet, if you
don't want to,
I'd be happy to go talk to him.
Daddy, I don't think Aoi
wants to be the king.
But you know that
she's not a quitter.
You should just
let her drop out.
Okay, then. Love ya, sweetie!
Sure, he talks
about "royal duty,"
but he just wants
us to be happy.
[AOI] I know he does but
dropping out of the election
isn't as easy as
you make it sound.
Wow.
You're willing to wear the crown
even if it makes you miserable?
Kanade. Why're you being
so mean about this?
You used to be such
a sweet little girl.
Aoi! Wanna go outside and play?
Yeah, whatever!
Ahem.
Okay, talk to me, I want to
know what your power is.
The real one.
You're being silly.
You know my power.
You have perfect memory,
thanks to Invisible Work.
And it's an impressive
ability, that's for sure.
Everything comes easy to you.
You've aced every
test you've taken.
You remember every
person you meet.
And you've memorized every
national statute word-for-word.
But that's your intelligence,
it's not magic.
What happened to my cute sister?
You were always so sweet.
I made this just for you, Aoi!
I'm still sweet, okay?
So why are you asking me now?
I've been waiting.
But I'm not very patient
and I wanna know what it is.
'Cause I know it's not long
before you turn the tide on me.
[AOI]
Wha...?
I wouldn't worry
about it, Kanade.
You'll surpass me soon enough.
[KANADE]
I hope you're right about that.
[AOI] She's right, I could turn
the tides and win the election
if I used my real power.
But I can't do that.
I won't abuse this
gift I've been given.
[NANAO]
Hello? Earth to Aoi!
[gasps]
You want us to post
these in front
of the freshman classrooms, too?
Uh. Yeah, I guess so.
Sorry to make you help. I can
put the rest up by myself.
We don't mind and you'll
get it done a lot faster.
For sure!
And besides, I don't
understand why you're stuck
doing this in
the first place.
Well, nobody else
wanted to do it.
I'm always happy to help out.
[UZUKI]
That's so like you!
Hey, look! Princess Aoi's
putting up posters today!
[STUDENT A] Would you
expect any less of her?
[STUDENT B] She's got three
other girls to help her out!
[STUDENT C]
Don't get in their way!
Geez, everyone's staring at us
like we're in some
kind of parade.
I'm sorry!
They've been at it since
elementary school.
Don't you remember, Shizuru?
Even back then everyone would
watch us walk down the hallway.
Yeah, I guess so.
Not that it was ever
limited to school.
Remember the lady who used
to call Aoi "Momotaro"?
If Aoi's Momotaro, then
Uzuki's the pheasant,
'cause she's so tiny.
That makes sense to me.
[NANAO]
So Shizuru's the monkey.
[SHIZURU] No, I'm the dog!
You're the monkey!
Uh, why don't you let
me be the monkey?
'Kay, then I get to
be Momotaro! Sweet!
Quit yappin', puppy!
I'm more Momotaro than you!
Isn't that right, Aoi?
[NANAO]
Told you so!
[SHIZURU]
Whatever.
You're just mad you got
stuck with the monkey.
[NANAO]
Better that than the dog!
[UZUKI] I think I would
make the best Momotaro.
[SHIZURU, NANAO]
You're the pheasant, Uzuki!
[UZUKI]
Okay, okay!
[NANAO]
You guys, guess what?
My friend's dog had
puppies a few days ago
and I went over to her
house to see them.
When I reached down to pet one,
it licked my finger and it was,
like, the cutest thing ever!
That's adorable.
Show us how it licked you.
[NANAO]
Huh? No way! That's super weird.
C'mon, Nana, show us.
[NANAO]
Huh?
Yes. Of course I will.
[gasps]
The student council asked
me to put up posters.
You guys wanna help?
[ALL]
Yes, of course we will.
Welcome home, Princess Aoi.
[AOI] Pardon me, sir.
May I ask you something?
Uh, sure.
I'm happy to help in
any way that I can.
[AOI]
Uh.
Well, I...
Would you please do a handstand
and bark like a dog for me?
[BODYGUARD]
Yes, of course I will.
[BODYGUARD barks]
[DOCTOR]
The examination concludes
that Princess Aoi's true power
is not the quick learning
and faultless memory
that she possesses.
Her actual power's called
"Absolute Obedience."
She can command immediate
loyalty of anyone.
Since she's been unaware
of this ability until now,
it's possible she's been using
it involuntarily for some time.
I suspect the commands
have gained power
throughout her adolescence,
which is why they
went unnoticed.
Her abilities have grown.
She did not always have absolute
control, but she does now.
Ah. Well, whatever
powers she has,
she'll always be my perfect
and beautiful princess.
Dad, stop you're
embarrassing me.
[AOI]
"Absolute Obedience."
That's the real power
that I possess.
Whenever I give a command,
people are forced to obey me.
No one should have
that kind of power.
Especially not someone
who could become king.
We're done, Aoi!
Thanks for all of your help.
[SHIZURU]
No big deal.
Uh. I'd really like to take
you to tea after school.
To thank you for helping me.
No way.
Not a chance.
Sorry. I guess you
have other plans.
It wasn't fair for me
to ask out of the blue--
We'll go if you agree
to split the bill.
We told you we would help you
out and we're happy to do it.
There's no need for you to
take us out. It's all good.
Yeah, you can always
bank on us to be there
when you need someone
to lend a hand.
We're your friends.
That's what we're here for.
[SHIZURU]
Sweet! Let's go.
[NANAO] Oh, we should go
for pancakes instead!
[UZUKI] Yeah! That's like
the best idea ever!
[AOI]
Wait for me!
[AOI] Ever since I found
out about my power,
I've worried that my friends
were just following my commands.
But now I know better.
[NANAO]
Hey, isn't that Akane?
[UZUKI]
It is her!
[AKANE]
Big Sister!
[NANAO]
Wow, look at you, Akane.
Walking home by yourself.
[AKANE] I'm trying to be more
independent but it's not easy.
I heard you're doing
some campaigning, too.
Aw, I'm so proud of you!
I can't believe you're the shy,
little princess we grew up with.
Yeah, you've gotten
brave. Good job.
That does it! You're
getting my vote for king!
Well, this is where
we split up. Later!
See you tomorrow!
[AOI]
'Kay, see you then.
[AKANE] You've got
great friends, y'know?
Yeah, I certainly do,
but sometimes I'm afraid
it's only because of my power.
[AKANE]
Uh?
Never mind me.
Come on. Sis, tell me
what's on your mind.
It's okay. I promise
I won't tell anybody.
Are you worried that
your friends only like you
because you're a princess?
[AOI]
Huh?
I mean, that might be
what drew them to you.
But anyone can see that the four
of you are best friends now.
It's true.
They love you for who you are,
not because of your
royal heritage.
[AOI]
Yeah. You're right.
That's funny!
I know, right?
Um. Hi. Sorry to bother you.
But, uh. My name's
Aoi Sakurada, and...
...I was wondering if I could
be friends with you guys.
[NANAO]
Sure. Sounds good.
Nice to meet you!
I think that we'll
make great friends.
[AOI]
Me too!
[AOI] I'm the Sakurada
family's first daughter, Aoi.
[SATSUKI]
My Aoi is compassionate,
with a big smile and
an even bigger heart.
She's always helping
keep the house in order.
[AOI]
Thanks, Mom,
but, honestly, I'm just glad
to help out however I can.
[SATSUKI] She's is a great
candidate for the throne
but what I want most
is for her to be happy.
I want you to choose
your own path, my dear.
[AOI] But sometimes the path we
walk is already chosen for us.
Anyway, if I had to
pick a favorite king,
I'd say Edward VIII,
I hope you'll give me your
vote. Thank you so much.