Living room, all clear.
Hall closet, all clear.
Bathroom, all clear.
[GUARD 7D]
Attic, all clear.
Basement, all clear.
[AKANE] To say that
our father, the king,
is overprotective
is an understatement.
He's always worried
about us kids.
Front entryway, all clear.
Back entry, all clear.
[GUARD 7H]
Kitchen, all clear.
Dad, who the heck are these men
and what are they
doing in our house?
What kind of father
do you think I am?
I'm going away for a
business trip overnight.
I can't leave three
of my daughters alone.
Soichiro, my love, you've always
been overly concerned.
We already went over this,
Dad, we'll be fine!
I'm just concerned.
Akane's down with a cold and
Shiori, well, she's so young.
You have to trust me.
We don't need guards.
I can take care
of them by myself.
Dear. I trust you.
I'd simply feel more comfortable
with the added security
of a few guards. That's all.
Like anyone would be dumb enough
to break into a house full
of people with superpowers.
[SOICHIRO]
Oh, I almost forgot!
We're going to need guards
at the end of the street, too.
Did you even listen to
a word that I just said?
[sighs] Honey...
[SOICHIRO] You think I'm
going overboard, too?
Well, at least let
this unit stay--
Nope, now hurry up
and get out of here
before I kick you out.
Ah! All right, fine.
But you have to promise me
one thing before I go, Kana!
What's that?
[SOICHIRO] Your power lets
you create anything
you can imagine while
the cost of that object
is withdrawn from
your bank account.
Promise me that, no matter
what, you will not create
anything that has yet
to be invented by man.
If you were to drain your
savings account again--
Daddy.
--Get out of here now.
--[SOICHIRO] Right!
[SATSUKI]
We're leaving, sweetie.
Come on, Soichiro, let's go.
[SOICHIRO]
Bye, Kana.
[sighs]
[SOICHIRO]
That's fine.
Just make sure your men
stick to the plan.
Yes, I'm aware of
the consequences
and I'll take
full responsibility.
Also, don't blow your cover.
[GUARD 7F]
Got it, Your Majesty!
[SATSUKI]
Seriously?
I can't believe you actually
called that ground unit.
Uh...
Well, you see, dear, it's
better to be safe than sorry.
Relax, you shouldn't worry
about Kanade so much.
She's grown into a very
responsible young lady.
[chuckles] As usual,
you're right.
Yeah.
What's Dad's deal?
He's the biggest
worrywart I know!
We can handle one night
alone. Can't we, Shiori?
I think so.
All right. It's time to
go and check on Akane.
[SHIORI]
Mm-hm.
[KANADE] Sorry, kiddo,
you have to stay here.
She could be
contagious and I don't
want you getting
sick on me, too.
Fine.
[KANADE] I hope she's
feeling a little better.
[AKANE screams]
Akane!
What's going on?
[AKANE sobbing]
[KANADE]
Are you in pain?
Please-- Tell me what's wrong!
He's dead!
But he was way too young
and handsome to die!
If you don't go back
to sleep right now,
you're gonna join him!
[beeping]
[KANADE]
How'd this happen?
Your temperature's
even higher now.
I'd better put one of those
fever patches on you.
Thanks for being
so nice to me today.
Whaddya mean? I'm
always nice to you.
[AKANE]
Yeah, you're awesome.
Well, thank you.
Hey. You know what?
[KANADE]
What?
I don't think you
need to act perfect
in front of everybody.
There's no need to pretend;
people will vote for you
'cause they like you
for who you are, y'know?
[KANADE] I dunno-- I mean,
look at who I'm up against.
There's no way I can beat Aoi
unless I'm a perfect angel.
What? You're silly.
Now, stop talking
and get some sleep.
[inahles] 'Kay.
[gasps] Shiori, what're
you doing out here?
I wanted to know if
Akane's feeling any better.
She'll be fine.
I gave her some medicine
and she's resting now.
Thank goodness.
Think she'll want something
to eat when she wakes up?
Probably.
Whaddya say we go cook up
something yummy for her?
'Kay!
I hope you stay sweet
like this forever, Shiori.
[SHIORI]
Huh?
[KANADE]
Mmm. Looking good.
You can turn the stove off now.
Okie doke.
[KANADE]
Ready to give it a try?
[SHIORI]
Yeah!
[KANADE]
It's tasty, right?
[SHIORI]
Mm-hm!
It's so yummy.
I'm sure Akane will feel
better once she eats it.
Think so?
[KANADE]
Definitely.
We're the best cooks ever.
[KANADE] What? How is it your
fever's gotten even higher?
Akane looks like she's in pain.
What am I supposed to do?
I know!
I'll create a medication that
can cure all her symptoms.
[SOICHIRO]
Promise me that no matter what,
you will not create
anything that has
yet to be invented by man.
If you were to drain your
savings account again--
[KANADE]
I know I shouldn't, Dad.
But still. What if
I could prevent
something horrible
from happening?
Kanade...
You okay?
[AKANE giggles]
I'm fine, I just have a cold.
You're making a big
fuss over nothing.
No. I'm not.
I don't need you to create
a cure-all pill for me.
Don't risk it,
I'll be okay as long
as I take my medicine
and get some rest.
No need to worry.
[KANADE]
I understand.
Instead, I'll bring to life the
smartest doctor to ever live.
[AKANE]
You don't understand anything!
If you create
anything to help me--
[KANADE]
What?
Then I'll run away.
And it'll be your fault.
[KANADE] Okay, okay, I get it!
Please don't do that!
[AKANE] All I'd have to
do is alter my gravity
and I could fly away and
you'd never see me again!
[KANADE] All right, fine!
I won't create anything.
Just lay back down.
[AKANE]
You pinky swear?
[KANADE]
I promise I won't!
--[AKANE] Sounds iffy.
--[KANADE] You need rest!
Put your head on your pillow!
Hey, I told you
not to come in here
unless you wanna
get sick. Shiori!
It's a magical kiss
to make you feel better.
[groans, giggles]
Shiori.
Who taught you how
to use that magic?
The kiss?
That's what Mommy and Daddy do
whenever I'm not feeling good.
[gasps] That's pretty
sweet. I never knew.
[KANADE] And they lived happily
ever after. The end.
All right, Miss Shiori.
It's way past your bed time
now. Aren't you tired yet?
[SHIORI] Can I stay up
just a little longer?
We can stay up late
but it's our secret, okay?
Yay!
[clatter]
Weird. Was that Akane?
I'll go and check it out.
[SHIORI]
Okay.
[KANADE]
Akane, how ya doing?
[gasps] She's not here.
I wonder if she
went to the bathroom.
[clatter]
[KANADE gasps]
Be careful, Kanade.
That noise was spooky.
[door creaks]
[SHIORI]
Akane, you scared me!
Sorry. Where'd Kana go?
[clattering]
[BOTH gasp]
Hey, Akane. Is that
you making noise?
Please answer me!
[gasps]
[screaming]
[KANADE gasps]
[KANADE]
Shu, what are you doing here?
I had to come back to pick up
some stuff that I forgot.
--[yelps]
--[GUARD 7A] Go! Go! Go! Go!
[AKANE, SHIORI gasp]
[GUARD 7B] Princess Akane and
Princess Shiori are safe.
[GUARD 7C]
Shower, all clear!
[GUARD 7D]
Toilet, all clear!
[GUARD 7E]
I've secured Sir Borscht!
[GUARD 7F] Princess Kanade,
have you been harmed?
[gasps]
[GUARD 7F] There was no
threat inside the house.
It may have been a false
alarm, but stay alert.
[KANADE]
You jerks are the threat!
[SOICHIRO] You idiots
rushed in?! How could you!
Did I not stress the
importance of being discreet?!
[GUARD 7F]
I apologize, Your Majesty.
I'd like to talk
to my dad please.
[SOICHIRO] No, don't do it!
Don't give it to her!
[GUARD 7F]
Uh, here you go.
[SOICHIRO groans] Oh, Kanade, my
darling. How are things going?
You couldn't trust me
for one night, Daddy?
[SOICHIRO] That's not it at all!
You see, there was a-- a--
Yeah, whatever you say.
We'll talk about this when
you get home tomorrow.
[KANADE]
You can have your toy back now.
[GUARD 7F] I apologize for
the scare earlier, Princess.
[AKANE giggles]
[KANADE sighs] Am I the only one
who got tired all of a sudden?
[AKANE giggles]
We should get some sleep.
[AKANE]
Yeah.
Wait. I forgot about Shiori.
She can't sleep in here or
she might catch your cold.
[AKANE]
I understand.
You sure?
Don't worry about me, I'm fine.
Shiori needs you more than I do.
[KANADE]
But you're sick.
It's okay.
[KANADE groans]
You better go, or I'll
run away for real this time.
[laughs] Fine, you win.
All right, Shiori.
It looks like I'll be joining
you in here tonight.
[SHIORI]
No!
Huh?
Akane's the sick one, not me.
She needs her big sister there
to help her feel better.
I can sleep fine
all by myself, Kana!
She kicked me out of her room.
[AKANE]
Uh...
[KANADE]
She finally got to sleep.
'Kay. I should go
check on Shiori.
I hope that you
feel better soon, sis.
I'm coming in, invited or not.
Better not let her catch me.
I don't wanna get scolded
by my little sister again.
Love you, Momma.
[KANADE]
She is pretty adorable though.
I think I'll keep her.
[AUDIENCE cheering]
Hello, fans!
[AKANE] Hikari has transformed
herself into an idol
by the name of Laito
Sakurapa in the hopes
of boosting her campaign.
[MATSUOKA]
What do ya think?
You gotta admit, she's turning
into a bona fide idol, right?
[SACCHY]
Sure.
I know she's a little
rough around the edges,
but, the girl's got talent.
[SACCHY]
She certainly has something.
And the rivalry between
you has been great.
The label couldn't have
asked for better publicity.
Don't you think? Sachiko?
Yes.
You really failed
the test! That sucks.
You prob'ly should've
studied a bit harder.
Hey, why don't you shut it?
She's got more important
responsibilities than school.
Yeah, being royalty
is hard work. Right?
It is.
[HIKARI] If only they knew
I didn't study 'cause
I'm too busy being an idol.
Don't you worry about
this stupid test.
Me, worried? Yeah, right. See--
I only put in 90% total
effort on this one!
[STUDENTS] Whoa, seriously?
You should've studied!
[HIKARI]
Hi, Matsuoka!
Ah-- I-- Hello there,
Princess Hikari.
I hope you're feeling well
after your recent performance.
To be honest, I'm kinda sick...
[MATSUOKA] Oh no, Princess!
We can't have that.
...of being called Princess.
[MATSUOKA]
Ahem. Sorry about that.
Whaddya say we go over
the video of your concert?
[HIKARI]
I'd love to!
There's no doubt
you're talented.
But you know, there's more to
being an idol than just talent.
Let's start with basic
training. To help you focus.
[HIKARI] But I've got
so much homework to do.
They really overload
us at school.
[MATSUOKA] First lesson: Don't
talk with your mouth full.
[HIKARI muffled mumbling]
[MATSUOKA] Sorry, I didn't
understand a word.
Listen.
I'm not saying you have to
be the perfect role model.
It's actually better for
your career if people
see that you have
flaws like them.
Do the fans want perfection?
No, they want an
idol who's relatable.
Now, about the show--
Hey, Matsuoka!
Hello, Sacchy!
Wait, I wasn't done
talking to you!
Havin' a good day?
It's been going great.
That is, until now.
Uh-- Ah.
Well, if she's not
into high fives...
[MATSUOKA]
Listen up!
I have some plans I
need to run by you two.
Sachiko's our biggest
star right now.
She's got a fan base.
And that's exactly what
Laito needs to build.
She needs to be exposed
to a wider audience.
You understand?
Which is the reason
why we've planned
a double concert for you.
[BOTH]
Double concert?
You heard me.
Together, you'll
be "Search Light"!
I'm gonna shoot
straight with you--
This is all about
boosting sales.
We're hoping that a double
ticket will do that.
So we'll both be on stage
performing songs together?
What? No way!
[MATSUOKA]
Sorry Sachiko, but Laito will be
headlining this
concert with you.
I need your support
to make this a success.
All I'm asking for is
a one-day collaboration.
But there will be a matinee
and an evening performance.
We need both shows to sell out.
After all, we're promoting it
as the concert of the year.
Are you in?
Well yeah, I guess so.
I'm excited!
[MATSUOKA] With good reason!
This is a big deal!
Hey, Sacchy! Are you pumped?
This is, like,
the coolest thing ever!
I can't wait to get
on that stage with you!
Yeah, whatever.
Huh?
Thing is, I sat down
and watched the video
of your last concert.
[HIKARI]
You did? That's so sweet of you!
What did you think?
[SACCHY] Honestly, it was
one of the worst I've seen.
It was a very sloppy performance
full of rookie mistakes.
Ah...
It's clear to me
that you don't take
being an idol seriously.
You come across overly
confident up on stage.
Almost smug-- It was bad.
[gasps]
That said.
I'll perform in
the double concert
because I take my job seriously.
Oh. Okay, then.
Sacchy...
I've got lessons now.
I'll see ya.
Wait, don't go!
[SACCHY]
Sorry, Laito.
But you need to learn that
raw talent isn't enough.
You have to work
hard to succeed.
Something tells me you've never
had to work hard for anything.
What'd I do to make
Sacchy mad at me?
[MATSUOKA] I know how you can
win her over as a friend.
[HIKARI whines unintelligibly]
[MATSUOKA] I'm sorry,
I can't understand you.
[whines louder]
[MATSUOKA]
Lemme explain, Laito.
Sachiko started out
with nothing.
She didn't have any powerful
connections to get ahead.
Nor did she have
amazing raw talent.
She pushed herself and
she never missed a lesson.
She started at the bottom
and she struggled to the top.
Sacchy had a dream,
and she worked hard
to make it a reality.
You can be just
as good as she is
if you train hard. Got it?
[HIKARI]
Yeah.
[COACH 7A]
One, two, three, four.
'Kay, I'm here to learn!
[COACH 7A]
That's enough for today.
I'll see you tomorrow.
[HIKARI yelps]
Do you mind if I stay and
practice a little longer?
Yeah! I'll stay, too!
[HIKARI] Unfortunately, Sachhy
hasn't said a word to me
since that day.
But, eventually, she'll notice
how hard I've been
working. She has to!
[AKANE]
Hey, um, Hikari?
If it's not a pain, could
you pretty, please get me
tickets to one of your
double concert shows?
Sure.
Oh, thank you!
And do you think, maybe,
you could take me backstage
and introduce me to... Sacchy?
[HIKARI]
Nope.
[AKANE whines]
[HIKARI] I can get you
tickets into the concert
but we can't hang
out or anything.
People can't find out
my true identity.
[HIKARI] I want to become
a great performer
based on my talent,
not because of who I am.
That'll earn me
Sacchy's respect.
Guess ya tried this time, huh?
'Cause that's an awesome score!
Whoa!
You're so smart, Hikari!
Ha!
We've only just begun to
tap into my true potential!
Hey, Sacchy? You should stop.
Don't wear yourself out
before the big concert.
True.
But I haven't nailed down
the choreography yet.
[SACCHY] I've gotta be
perfect and show Laito
that raw talent is no
match for hard work.
Whoa!
[SACCHY]
Hey, Sakurapa.
Yeah?
[SACCHY] I wanted you
to know that I'm not
going to sabotage
today's concerts.
I'm not here to
hurt your career.
But I also won't be performing
to help increase your sales.
So I'll sing,
but I'll be doing it
for the fans out there.
I plan on giving them a
show they'll never forget.
Like a true idol would.
You're reading my
mind right now!
Let's go out on that stage
tonight and make this
the best concert that
they've ever seen!
Huh?
[SACCHY] I didn't expect that
kind of reaction from her.
Now I look like
the conceited jerk.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[SACCHY, HIKARI]
Welcome to the show!
That was seriously awesome!
You two put on the best
concert I've ever seen!
[SACCHY]
Thank you.
We really gave it
our best out there.
[MATSUOKA]
And it showed!
Shoot for that
kind of performance
for the evening show!
Will do, sir.
That goes for you, too!
What? Oh. Yeah.
Laito, were you listening?
No, I really wasn't.
--[MS. YAMAMOTO] Ah...
--[MATSUOKA] Uh-huh.
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[SACCHY] Two concerts in one day
is a lot harder than I thought.
I'm impressed with how well
Sakurapa is holding up.
She's really good.
You can tell that she's taking
these concerts seriously.
But what happens
to me when someone
with her talent
puts in the effort?
I have to try harder.
I have to be better
than her! I have to!
[SACCHY yelps]
No! Sacchy!
[SACCHY whimpers]
[HIKARI] Do you think
you'll ever walk again?
What're you talking about?
I just sprained it!
I'm gonna be fine.
I understand. Thank you, Doc.
Hey, Sachiko, bad news.
[BOTH gasp]
You can't go back on stage.
You could risk permanent
damage to your ankle.
[SACCHY]
What? That's crazy!
You can't stop me
from performing!
I can!
I won't have you risking
the rest of your career!
Sacchy, please listen to me.
Don't try to fight me on this.
As for you, Laito.
The show must go on.
I need you to go and finish
the concert by yourself.
Huh?
[MATSUOKA]
I know it's a lot to ask,
but you've proven
yourself today.
Please, Laito.
[HIKARI]
Okay.
[gasps]
Let's do this!
Hey, guys! Sorry about
the short delay!
Let's get this concert
back on track!
Who wants to hear some music?
All right! Then I'm
gonna kick it off with--
[grunts]
[HIKARI giggles]
I'm so clumsy!
[AUDIENCE laughs]
[HIKARI] I'm excited to sing our
new song for you. It's called:
"Follow The Search Light!"
[singing in Japanese]
I hope you're watching, Sacchy!
[gasps]
[HIKARI] The fans and I sure
do miss you out here!
I need to apologize
for the mean things
I've said to you.
I was so focused on trying
to show you up, that--
I forgot the fans.
What? You have no
reason to apologize.
You were right, I wasn't
giving it my all.
[SACCHY] I gotta admit,
you put on a wonderful show.
You think so? I mean,
I took that tumble.
No big, you made it look good.
Oh, really? Thank you, Sacchy!
I can tell you had fun and
that's what's important.
Yup.
Idols don't have to be perfect
to put on a good concert.
You've just gotta
have fun out there.
'Cause that's what
the fans wanna see.
At least I think so.
That's what Mr. Matsuoka
always tells me.
Right?
I misjudged you. I'm sorry.
You're gonna be an awesome idol.
[gasps]
And...
Well, um-- I feel silly asking
after the way I've acted--
But would you be willing
to be my rival and friend?
Because that would
make me really happy.
[gasps, shrieks]
It's all I've ever wanted!
We'll be best friends
forever and together,
we'll rise to the top of
the entertainment industry!
Are you ladies okay?
What's up?
[MATSUOKA]
Oh, um.
There seems to be
an intruder backstage
peeping into the dressing rooms.
How'd they get back here?
I dunno!
The intruder moved so
fast it was almost like
they could defy gravity.
Our security guards
couldn't even
get close enough to catch 'em.
Did you say gravity?!
[TERU] I'm Teru, third son of
the Sakurada royal family.
That's T-E-R-U.
[SATSUKI]
Teru's a bit of a daredevil.
Needless to say, I spend
a lot of time worrying
about the little guy.
[TERU]
What?!
[SATSUKI] If Teru were to become
king, he wouldn't think twice
about risking his life
to save his people.
What's your campaign
slogan again, dear?
[TERU] I will protect this
country and its citizens
with my own two fists!
How could you ever forget
that awesome slogan?
And, just to remind
everyone, Napoleon was
the coolest king ever.
Don't forget to get out on
election day and vote for me!