Huh?
[screams]
[AKANE]
Are you okay, citizen?
Yeah, I am!
Thought I was a goner! Thanks!
[AKANE] I only did what
was right. Whoosh!
Whenever calamity strikes,
just call my name!
In the royal garden of
Castle Town, I bloomed.
Like a rose petal,
gracefully riding
the winds of justice, I fly.
Thank you so much, Pr--
[AKANE]
Listen up! This rose has thorns.
I'm Scarlet Bloom!
[SALARYMAN 9A]
Huh.
[AKANE] Hello and thank
you all for coming.
My name is Akane Sakurada, and I
want to become the next king
of our great country,
so that I can protect
the peace of every citizen.
[applause]
Good!
Did I already say that
my name is Akane Sakurada?
So, um, if I am elected king,
I promise to carry out
the following three points.
[shrieks] Why is the news here?
This is great, Akane!
Media coverage is
a good thing, right?
Yeah, but--
Go on!
First, I will ban the use
of surveillance cameras.
They've been a plague on
our privacy for too long.
And once they're gone,
everybody will be able
to live peaceful...
happy... lives...
[AKANE] I can't take
all this staring!
You can do it! Just trust me.
So that is my solemn
promise to each of you
and I would really appreciate
it if you'd vote for me.
[FUKUSHINA]
Vote for Akanee!
[BOY STUDENTS]
Vote for Akane!
[AKANE]
Thank you. And, uh-- Goodbye!
[sighs]
[AOI] I'm glad Akane finally
worked up the nerve
to go out and campaign.
But she's so frazzled
in front of the crowd
that she can barely
talk, and she never
makes eye contact with them.
She's fifth in the
opinion polls this week,
so the public speaking isn't
really helping her cause.
There must be something
else we can try.
[ROSE TYPHOON]
The masked heroine,
Rose Typhoon Double X has
arrived! Beware, villains!
[TV NARRATOR 9A]
Rose Typhoon Double X protects
the peace of the people from
behind her crimson mask!
No one knows her true identity.
For she is really Hanae, the
clumsiest girl in her class!
They must be dumb. It's
totally obvious it's her.
Please don't say that!
If anyone finds out it's her,
she'll turn into a rabbit
and the show will end!
But wouldn't they be
grateful if they knew?
I bet she'd be really
popular after that!
[gasps] Eureka!
[TERU, SHIORI, HIKARI]
Hm?
[KANADE] Wait, you wanna
make Akane a superhero?
[AOI]
Yes.
If she hides her identity,
she can protect people
without her shyness
getting in the way.
After a while, she could
reveal herself to the public
and her popularity will
shoot through the roof.
Also...
[KANADE]
Go on.
I'm starting to worry
about her future
and what it holds for her.
And I'm not just talking
about the election.
Her social anxiety could
cause major hardships for her
once she's out on her own.
She's been working so hard.
Desperately trying to
change in her own way.
She needs confidence!
If she can learn to be
assertive in front of others,
I know she'll eventually
get over her shyness.
[KANADE]
Wait here.
Thanks, Kana!
[AOI gasps]
That was fast.
[KANADE]
Here.
[AOI]
Glasses?
[KANADE]
Jamming Glasses.
All she has to do is
wear these and no one
will be able to recognize
her. Instant masked hero.
That's the only
pair you get, okay?
Thanks a lot, Kana.
They're perfect.
I hope your bank account
didn't take too much of a hit.
[KANADE]
No big.
[AOI] I can't help but think
these are just an old pair
she grabbed from her bedroom.
What, they're not
good enough for you?
[AOI] No, they're fine!
Seriously! Thank you!
[KANADE] I did take some steps
to reduce the overall cost.
They'll only work if Akane
is the person wearing them.
Plus, they won't be as effective
on people who know her.
But strangers are fine.
If you don't believe me,
you could come up
with another plan.
[AOI]
No, I believe you! I swear!
Now please give them back!
[AKANE]
'Kay. How do I look?
Uh. Great.
Awesome! Okay.
Let's test 'em out!
Yeah.
Recognize her? Think.
[SHU]
Of course! It's Aka--
Just play along
with her. Understand?
[SHU]
Fine.
Sorry, have we met before?
No way! He can't tell!
You started to say her name.
But I can tell...
that you're adorable.
'Kay, See you later, Shu.
Can you guess who this is?
[TERU]
Uh...
[AOI]
Nothing?
She's a stranger.
A stranger. Yeah.
Are you sure?
[TERU] I'd better be lying
for a good reason, Kanade.
You'll see Akane
wearing glasses.
When you do, I want you to
pretend like she's a stranger,
you got it?
[SHIORI] I have to lie
for my big sister's sake.
You want her to stop
being so shy, don't you?
[whimpers]
Hey. What's wrong?
Shiori?
Now you made her cry!
She's probably afraid
of this total stranger
you brought in our house!
Don't cry! It's me, Akane!
[TERU]
I had no idea!
[AKANE] I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
[TERU] That's one
awesome disguise, sis.
[AOI]
Operation Masked Hero is a go.
[GIRL 9A] Mister! The poor
kitty's stuck up there!
He's too afraid to come
down, you have to help!
[FUKUSHINA]
That's pretty high.
I'm not sure we can get him.
[AKANE]
I'll do it!
[meows]
Oh, wow!
Isn't that--?
No way.
[AKANE] There. Now,
try not to climb so high.
[CAT 9A meows]
Thanks for saving the kitty!
'Scuse me.
You'll have to forgive me
if I'm mistaken, but,
aren't you Sakura--
[AKANE]
Whoosh!
I am...
You are what?
[AKANE] The rose of justice--
The one and only Scarlet Bloo...
[gasps]
Oh, I get it! That's a
nice cosplay. Aka--
Thank you! You really
saved the day!
Yeah, you did!
Kitty would've been
stuck forever!
Have no fear!
Scarlet Bloom is here!
[FUKUSHINA]
Hooray!
[BOY 9A]
Huh?
[AKANE] Be sure to
watch out for poachers!
[AKANE] So this is how it
feels to get out and live!
[FUKUSHINA]
You're a hero to people
and animals everywhere!
I only did what was
necessary, citizen.
Let's salute the
rose of justice!
[BOY STUDENTS] Scarlet Bloom
is the best in the world!
Oh, you guys!
[AOI] Well? Is there
anyhing online yet?
[HARUKA] Yeah. She's an
internet sensation!
[AOI gasps]
This one was recent.
[MISAKI] That's crazy!
How'd they even get this shot?
Scarlet Bloom's been
trending on Tweetbook
and MyFace, too.
She's a household name.
Wow.
[AOI] What do you know?
It's really working!
[NEWSCASTER 1A]
Another appearance by Aka--
Oh, e-hem-- Scarlet Bloom,
resulted in cheers. And a
couple of very happy whales!
The red-haired hero's
true identity
is still a mystery. Any ideas?
[MR. MASHIMA]
She's just Scarlet Bloom to me.
[NEWSCASTER 1B] In other news,
the June election polls
have been tallied.
You might be shocked.
That's right, Princess Akane,
who was recently in fifth,
has moved up in the ranks.
Putting some pressure on
Kanade in second place.
Your score's
looking good, Akane.
Heh. Yeah.
Since I started wearing
the mask, it's gone up.
Scarlet Bloom is doing
wonders for my campaign.
Wait.
How am I getting this popular
when I'm hiding my identity?
[AOI]
Speeches!
Your public rallies
are starting to pay off!
[AKANE]
Oh, yeah. I forgot about those.
Well, you must be
feeling hungry. Want cake?
--I do!
--[AKANE] Sure.
[SHU] Y'know, watching you
as Scarlet Bloom reminds me
of when you were a kid, Akane.
"I'll protect everyone
in this town from evil!"
You were such a feisty rascal.
[TERU] Whoa, for real?
That's so awesome, sis!
Well. That was a long time ago.
[SHU]
Behold the red rose of justice!
[AKANE yelps]
Knock it off!
Geez, why're you so
embarrassed about it?
[AKANE] I'm not when I'm
Scarlet Bloom, but right now,
I'm just plain old Akane,
so you'd better stop
before I totally freak out!
[groans] I guess I should
be glad that only you guys
know my secret.
Wow. You really are dense.
Everyone and their dog
knows that it's y--
[AOI]
Hey, Hikari.
I'd like to have a little
chat with you, please.
[HIKARI whimpers]
[AKANE] You got quiet.
What did you two talk about?
Oh. Nothing.
What's wrong? Aren't
you gonna eat?
[HIKARI]
Not hungry. Want it? Here.
You can have the
rest, Miss Bloo--
[AOI]
Hikari...
I think we need to have
another little chit-chat.
[HIKARI]
'Kay.
[AKANE] I feel bad that
you're wasting your Sunday
to help me out.
[KAREN] It's fine. I'm
kind of shocked, though.
You never want to
go for groceries.
[laughs nervously]
You sure about this?
We can leave.
No! It's totally cool.
I can handle this.
After everything
I've done lately,
this should be a breeze, right?
[KAREN] I thought her
shyness was getting better
thanks to the whole
"Scarlet Bloom" thing.
[AKANE]
I'll be fine. Come on!
[KAREN] But she still
has a long way to go.
[GIRL 9B sobbing]
I'm slipping!
No!
Crap! Not good!
She can't hold on!
Go help her!
[gasps]
[GIRL 9B whimpers]
[screams]
Akane!
You did it!
[MOTHER 9A]
You're a hero.
Honestly, I can't
thank you enough.
[AKANE]
I'm just glad she's not hurt.
[MOTHER 9A]
Go on.
Don't you have
something to say to her?
Oh, uh. Yes, ma'am.
You're so cool!
Thank you, Scarlet Bloom!
[KAREN]
Hm?
You're welcome, sweetie!
Now do me a favor and don't
play on the balcony, okay?
[GIRL 9B]
I won't!
[KAREN]
Eh. She'll notice someday.
[AKANE]
I'm home!
You look happy.
Did something good happen today?
[AKANE]
Nah, nothing in particular.
Whoopsie! I left my
Jamming Glasses behind.
Wait. Then how did she know?
You're so cool!
Thank you, Scarlet Bloom!
Uh...
[AKANE]
It doesn't make any sense.
How could this happen?
Don't tell me she's
so popular now
that everyone thinks I'm her!
I wanna tell her the
truth more than anything.
But Aoi would strangle me.
[AKANE]
What am I supposed to do now?
[SOCCER PLAYER 9A]
Misaki!
I know it's sudden, but we
could really use Raio's help.
You mean right now?
[SOCCER PLAYER 9A]
Yeah. Sorry.
Sure! No prob.
Huh?
Oh! Thank you so much!
--Please. It's nothing.
--[TENNIS PLAYER 9A] Misaki!
Is Yuniko free
anytime this week?
Hang on, I'll check.
Yep! Every day except
for the weekend!
Wonderful!
Can we have her for
the next couple of days?
She's all yours!
[SOCCER PLAYER 9A]
I don't mean to rush you, but--
Oh, yeah.
Sorry, Haru, I'm gonna
be here for a while.
It can't be helped.
Guess I'll go home and start
writing your next speech.
[MISAKI]
Make sure it's awesome, 'kay?
[SOCCER PLAYER 9A]
We just went into overtime.
[HARUKA] Even though
she's got her hands full,
she's still willing
to help others.
Yet another reason I'm sure
she'll make a great king.
[MISAKI sighs] Watching Raio
play is exhausting!
[TERU] Hurry, Shiori!
It already started!
[NEWSCASTER 1B]
Princess Akane rose in rank
again this week.
Passing her sister, Princess
Kanade, for the second spot.
Way to go! That's amazing, sis!
--Wow. Thank you. Crazy.
--[NEWSCASTER 1A] We now take
you live to Prince
Shu's campaign rally.
[SATO]
Uh, hello all. Welcome!
Isn't this lovely
weather we're having?
It's the perfect evening
for a speech or two!
Hana. Try to relax.
Sorry! Uh. I'm done now.
[AKANE] Poor Hana. I heard
she's managing all of Shu's
campaign speeches lately.
[HARUKA sighs] I need to
find a way to make this one
stand out from the others.
[MISAKI]
I'm home.
'Bout time.
I could use your
help. Hear me out.
For the next speech,
I'd like to shift focus
to promoting your
clones and their, uh--
Hey. What's wrong?
I was thinking about
Shu and Akane.
They're both working so hard.
Yeah. You're right.
That's exactly why we
can't afford to slack off.
[MISAKI]
I dunno.
I'm not sure I deserve
to become king.
[HARUKA]
What are you talking about?
[MISAKI] To be honest, the only
reason that I wanna win,
is not necessarily
because I wanna rule.
I just thought it'd make
you appreciate me more.
I wanna be your favorite sister.
[gasps]
I mean, what kinda
king thinks like that?
You must be disappointed.
Why would you think that?
[MISAKI]
'Cause you support me.
Without you, I wouldn't
have any speeches to give
or any confidence
in my own abilities.
And yet, compared to
Akane and the others,
I might as well
be standing still.
They've come so far
and they did it
through their own efforts.
[HARUKA]
I'm not sure Akane did.
[MISAKI] Sorry, Haru, but I'm
just not fit to be the king.
[HARUKA]
You're the most fit to be king!
[MISAKI]
Huh?
[HARUKA]
You're a regular Joe.
That's why people feel
comfortable around you.
Let's see. How
should I put this?
Perspective. You see the
world through the same eyes
as every normal person
in this country.
[gasps]
[HARUKA] That's why you're the
best candidate for the throne.
That's what I think, anyway,
and it's why I support you.
But you would be a better
choice than I ever would.
[HARUKA] My talents are more
suited to an advisory role.
So that's what I've
decided to do.
Besides.
[gasps]
[HARUKA] You're no good
without me. Isn't that right?
Thanks, Haruka.
[MISAKI] He actually believes
that I could win this thing.
I don't wanna let him down.
So I'd better start
believing in me, too!
I may not be able to live up
to his ideal yet, but for now--
I will try. And I will win!
Good.
Then we should start
working on that speech--
[MISAKI] No. I'm writing
this one on my own.
It has to be me.
If they aren't my words,
then what's the point?
I can do it.
Yes, you can.
[REINDEER SUIT MAN 9A]
Merry Christmas!
Get your holiday cakes
before they're gone!
Gluten free available!
Time flies. Christmas
Eve is tomorrow night.
[AOI] I almost forgot.
My birthday's tomorrow.
The New Year will come and go
before we even realize it.
[MISAKI]
Hello, everyone.
I know you're super busy
shopping for the holidays,
but I could really
use your help.
I'm Misaki Sakurada,
and I would like to turn
our country into an
even brighter place
than it already is.
To be honest, I haven't
figured out how to do that.
Well, not yet.
But, with your help, I know
that we can work together
to achieve that goal.
That is my dream.
[NANAO] Whoa. Misaki's
all by herself today.
Yeah. She wanted to try
on her own this time.
[SHIZURU] Nice. She's not
even using her clones.
[UZUKI]
That's pretty cool.
[WOMAN 9A] Look! Princess Aoi
and her attendants!
[WOMAN 9B] She's probably
watching the rally.
[WOMAN 9C]
Or on business.
[WOMAN 9D]
We should stay out of her way.
Am I the only one with a
wicked case of déjà vu here?
It's not like it
happens every time.
Let's get going.
Right.
Sorry that happened.
[NANAO]
No big. We're used to it.
[UZUKI] Yeah! It doesn't
bother me at all!
[SHIZURU]
Nothing bothers you.
[AOI giggles] What should we
do now? You wanna go for tea?
I'm out.
My boss asked me to
cover a shift at work.
[AOI]
We can wait if it'll be quick.
Well,
I have to go to my club's
meeting afterwards, so, sorry!
Next time!
Bummer. She's so busy.
That girl is always
up to something.
What's new?
Her social circle's
gotten even bigger
since she started her job.
Oh, I see.
Well, I'm fine with just
the three of us hanging out
if you'd still
like to go get tea.
[SHIZURU]
I can't.
I have a couple of
errands I've gotta run.
[AOI] Is it anything
we could help with?
No, it's... uh...
Bye!
[AOI]
Uh... See ya later.
--Well, what about you?
--[yelps]
I'm sorry, Aoi.
Actually, I have to
deliver some medicine
to my sick aunt on
the other side of town.
I didn't know that
you had an aunt.
Uh! Maybe next time!
Okay. I'm sorry for
holding you up.
No. It's fine. Really! Later!
[AOI] I made the three of
them spend time with me
and never thought
about their lives.
It's always been the four of us.
I guess I just thought
that would never change.
But the truth is, if I
become king next year,
everything will be different.
Especially our social lives.
Being around me always seems
to cause trouble for them.
Maybe I shouldn't invite
them out as much.
I don't have the right to
monopolize their lives.
It's time I learned to
stand alone, like royalty.
Don't be sad! This is life!
You knew that you had
to grow up someday!
--Keep your chin up, Aoi!
--[phone vibrating]
[AOI]
It's from Shizu.
[SHIZURU] My errands
were suddenly cancelled.
You wanna come to my place
and hang for a bit?
[AOI]
Yes!
[GIRL 9C, BOY 9B]
Huh?
[SHIZURU]
Sorry this was so last minute.
[AOI] No worries. I really
wasn't doing anything.
[SHIZURU]
Well, I'm glad you came.
We rarely get any
one-on-one time together.
[AOI giggles] For real,
I'm looking forward to it.
[SHIZURU]
Mm... Could you give me a sec?
It's messy in here.
Oh, it won't bother me.
Remember, I have eight siblings.
[gasps]
Sorry, you probably have
personal items to clean up, huh?
What are you going on about now?
[AOI]
I can be ignorant sometimes.
I wasn't being sensitive.
Please, go ahead!
Okay.
[AOI]
I just realized.
It's been a long time since
I've been in Shizuru's room.
[cellphone vibrates]
[AOI]
Wow. That was fast.
I'm coming in.
[AOI gasps]
Why is it dark?
Hey. Where are you?
[ALL]
Surprise! Happy Birthday, Aoi!
[gasps]
[UZUKI]
Did you suspect us?
No. Not at all.
Good!
We thought you were on to us
after all our lame excuses.
We 've always wanted
to celebrate with you,
but that would intrude
on your family.
It might be a day early,
but, at least this way,
we get to celebrate it together.
--[AOI whimpers]
--[SHIZURU, UZUKI gasp]
Hey...
[UZUKI]
Aoi?
You guys. Thank you...
...so much.
Our pleasure.
Oh, and, you forgot
to take your shoes off.
Sorry!
Jeez. Shizu!
[SHIZURU] I'm starving.
This cake won't eat itself.
[NANAO]
Not yet, doofus!
She still needs to...
[AOI] Happiness is
different for everyone.
And it can take a
long time to find it.
But, as far as I'm concerned,
I don't have to look any
farther than right here.
I wish this feeling could
stay with me forever.
I'd give up everything
to make it happen.
Even the crown.
[SHIZURU, UZUKI, NANAO]
Happy birthday, Aoi!
[SHIZURU] Okay, she blew
them out. Can we eat now?
[UZUKI] No! The birthday girl
gets the first slice!
[NANAO]
Go ahead, Aoi. Pick one.
Uh... That one!
[NANAO] Darn it. I was
eyeing that strawberry.
[UZUKI]
You can have this piece, Nanao.
[AOI]
Then I'll take this one.
[SHIZURU]
Aw, that's mine!
--[UZUKI] Wow! Rude much?
--[AOI] For real.
[SHIZURU]
Rock, paper, scissors for it!
[NANAO]
No way!
[AKANE] All right.
Tomorrow is Christmas Eve.
So, we're throwing
Aoi a surprise party!
As you know, she has
always found out about it,
despite our best efforts.
That won't happen this year!
I need you to be extra diligent
in your duties, understood?
[SHIORI, TERU, HIKARI, MISAKI]
Roger!
[AKANE] I'll be counting on
your clones, in particular.
They're all yours, Akane!
[AKANE]
This is a top secret operation!
Anyone who spoils it will
pay the ultimate penalty!
We'll surprise her,
or die trying!
[SHIORI, TERU, HIKARI, MISAKI]
Yeah!
[AOI giggles]
[AKANE] I'm the rose of
justice, Scarlet Bloom!
[SATSUKI] When you were
younger, you used to play
superhero all the time,
but I always thought
you would grow out of it once
you got a little older.
[AKANE] It's fun to pretend
to be someone else for a while.
I feel like I can do things
I normally can't, you know?
Maybe I should start campaigning
for king as Scarlet Bloom!
[SATSUKI] But if you do,
she'll be the king,
and not my sweet Akane.
[AKANE]
Oh, good point.
Did you hear that, everyone?
Please do not write Scarlet
Bloom on your ballots!
If you do, they won't be valid!
And that would be
very bad for me!