[SATO] I can't believe
it's already fall.
[SHU]
Neither can I.
[SATO] Almost all of the
leaves have changed color!
[SHU]
Yeah.
You've been walking
me home like this
for a while now. It's like
I'm living a dream.
I know it's silly, but
sometimes I get so scared.
What if you're not
really here with me?
I mean, you could be an
illusion that disappears
into thin air at any moment.
[SHU gasps]
[screams]
[SATO]
I know, it's crazy.
Something like that
would never ha... ppen.
[SATO]
Huh? Sakurada!
[AOI sighs]
So, Aoi, everything all right?
Those pollen allergies
of yours seem to
spring up outta nowhere.
Be sure to take good
care of yourself, 'kay?
[AOI]
Uh-huh.
[KANADE grunting]
[AKANE]
Hey, Kana?
May I ask why you're
summoning so many rocks?
Because they're free. Duh.
[HARUKA] Tomorrow's weather
probability is 85% sun.
And the day after that,
it'll be cloudy--
But by the end of the
week, it'll clear up
and it'll be sunny.
[HIKARI] So, Misaki,
about all these clones...
[MISAKI]
There's nothing that I can do!
You'll just have to
deal with it, Hikari!
Must not destroy.
Gotta hold back the power!
Mr. Table?
I'm sorry we have to put
so many hot plates on you
during dinner. And, Ms. Chair,
thank you for the sitting,
even though it's not
a lot of fun for you, is it?
Hi, everyone. I'm--
[ALL chattering]
The Break Out got to
all of you guys, too.
It'll be all right.
It sucks that this
keeps happening to--
Kids.
Everyone, head upstairs--
Let's move it!
I'll let you know
when dinner's ready.
[ALL]
Okay!
[BORSCHT purring]
[sighs] You think everything
will be back to normal
by tomorrow night?
For sure!
Break Outs normally
last only a day or so--
we should be fine by then.
Good!
I'm so glad Laito doesn't
have a performance tomorrow.
[cellphone chimes]
An email.
[AKANE]
What?
[AKANE] This might not be the
best day for me to be outside.
Just gotta stay focused.
I am a little nervous
about meeting up
with Sato all alone.
I've gotta be brave,
or else I'm never
gonna survive the election.
Princess Akane!
Oh! Hey, Sato!
Sorry! I didn't mean to be late!
Were you waiting very long?
[AKANE]
No! Not at all!
[SATO shrieks]
It's all good. I just
showed up here myself!
[SATO]
You sure you're not angry?
I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
[AKANE]
No big deal, it's only soda.
I'm not mad, really! I must've
squeezed it too hard.
Sorry, we're in the
middle of a Break Out.
What's that? Sounds awful.
[AKANE] Sometimes our royal
superpowers go berserk
and we can't control
them for a little while.
Oh!
Well, that would explain
why your brother
disappeared on me yesterday.
Yeah!
It hit us out of nowhere, so I
bet Shu was having a hard time
keeping his power in check.
Sometimes, if it's
real bad, we actually
have to keep the family
quarantined for the entire time.
[laughs nervously]
[AKANE] But don't worry.
It hasn't been that bad today.
As long as I stay
focused, I should
be able to keep
it under control.
[SATO] You'll have to
focus harder than that!
I'm sorry for making you
go out at a time like this.
It's fine, really.
[SATO]
Thanks.
I'm glad you could meet me,
I wanted to ask your advice.
No prob.
There's one other thing.
The place I was thinking
about taking you is popular,
so it may be kinda crowded.
[AKANE]
That's perfectly fine with me!
I've decided that I'm
going to win this election!
Yeah, right, of course you have.
[WOMAN IN PARK 8A]
Hello, Princess Akane.
Good afternoon.
[AKANE whimpers]
And to you, ma'am.
But in order to do that,
I must overcome my crippling
fear of being in public!
[sighs]
[AKANE]
So, what's up?
I gotta admit, your email
kinda freaked me out.
Yeah, sorry about that.
I had more to say, but
I hit send on accident.
I hate to bother you, but
Shu-Shu said if I couldn't
talk about something with him,
I should ask one of his sisters.
And it seemed like a perfect
chance to talk to you,
so I figured why not?
[AKANE] Hang on a second.
What is "Shu-Shu"?
Is that a nickname or something?
Oh, well, yeah, but it's
not like I call him that
to his face or anything.
[AKANE] Don't get me
wrong, I'm flattered,
but why come to me?
I'm sure that you have
plenty of girlfriends
to talk to about Shu.
I talk to Hitomi sometimes, but,
other than her, I
haven't told anybody.
I guess, I thought you'd be
the perfect sister to talk to
because you already
know about us.
Well. I do spend
a lot of time with Shu.
I mean he's my brother, and
we're actually pretty close.
Wait.
You're in the same class
as Kanade, aren't you?
Why not talk to her?
Uh, oh, yeah.
[SATO] The thing is, Kanade's
kind of intimidating.
She scares me.
[AKANE]
I don't think it's a secret
that you guys like each other.
You've been talking for a while.
I mean, our family already
knows, so he probably
doesn't mind if word gets out.
I know. It's just--
I'm not that confident.
I was jealous.
You were walking with another
girl, and-- I like you!
[SHU]
Okay, then. I promise, Sato.
When the election is over,
I'll tell you how I feel.
[gasps]
[SATO] He told me he'd
return my feelings
and I know that's all
that should matter.
But what will people think
when they see a girl
like me with a prince?
What if they say mean things?
And what about his fangirls?
Will they still root for him?
What if it affects the election?
[AKANE]
Good point.
Except you're the
only girl who's ever
fallen for that goofball.
[SATO]
I confessed my feelings to him
because I had to be honest.
But if doing that is
somehow holding him back...
It's not worth it.
[AKANE] I've never really
thought about it, but--
It's gotta be tough
for normal people
to hang around with a
member of the royal family.
[gasps]
Ah! Nothing. Just.
Well, are we almost there?
Ah! Yeah! We're super close.
It's around this
next corner, I swear!
[WAITRESS 8A]
I'm so sorry, ladies.
But I'm afraid we're
suddenly very busy.
All we have available
are seats on the patio.
If you wouldn't mind
waiting for a bit,
we'll gladly put something
together for you.
Oh, no! Please!
Don't go out of your
way for us. We're good.
[AKANE]
It's another challenge.
If I wanna be king, I'm gonna
have to talk in front of
way bigger crowds than this.
People will see me
eat as they walk by.
I can do this!
What are you talking about?
[SATO] Sounds like it's
tough for you guys, too.
Still, the way you're
trying to show everyone
who you really are is admirable.
[AKANE]
Huh?
I could never do
anything like that.
I don't have the
courage to stand up
and make people take notice.
That's why I was so
surprised when your brother
remembered me, even though
he hadn't seen me
since the fourth grade.
I mean, there are people
who were in my class
just last year who still
have no idea who I am.
But he remembered.
And I fell head
over heels for him!
Wow. That's all it took?
It's Princess Akane!
What's she having?
Lemme see!
[WOMAN 8A] I'm gonna order
one of those right now!
[MAN 8A]
Make it two!
I thought this patio
suddenly felt crowded.
I'm sorry about this.
You were so sweet to
invite me out with you.
It isn't fun, but this is
what it's like to be a royal.
Wait, what are
you talking about?
It a hassle to go out anywhere.
And when you do go out,
it's virtually impossible
to get any privacy.
If you don't like
being in the spotlight,
then you'll have
to deal with that
before you can marry my brother
Marry? Whoa!
Who said anything
about marriage?
We haven't even been on
our first date yet, silly!
Uh...
Ah-- What do you say we dig in?
Sounds like a plan to me!
[SATO]
You okay?
Uh...
[AKANE shrieks]
Oh my gosh, are you all right?
[whimpering]
[AKANE] Oh, no!
Everyone's staring at me!
Please stop looking at me!
If you don't, I'll lose focus!
[screams]
[gasps]
Don't worry I'll distract
everyone for you.
Sneak off and get
inside the café.
Thank you so much!
You're my hero!
You ready?
Hey, everyone!
My name is Hana Sato and I've
got an important announcement!
You don't know me
but I'm a classmate
and friend of the eldest prince!
I decided to step it up
a notch. That's right!
I confessed my feelings
to Prince Shu Sakurada!
[CROWD gasping]
He's not the type
to rush into things,
so we're going slow.
Well, for now.
But when the election's
over, he will be mine!
You bet I'm gonna
date that prince
and after that,
I'm gonna marry him!
[CROWD cheers]
[AKANE] You saved me today.
Two times, in fact.
I promise I'll pay you
back for the clothes.
Please. I was happy
to help you out.
Ah. I can't believe it.
Once I started talking,
I couldn't stop myself.
I hope he doesn't turn around
and dump me over this.
[AKANE]
I don't think that'll happen.
If I were him, I'd be flattered.
Earlier today, you told me that
you weren't very
brave or confident.
But you're confident about
your feelings for Shu.
What you did was brave!
Do you think so?
Yeah, I do.
Promise you'll take
good care of him?
[gasps] Oh. Um, right!
[chuckles]
[AKANE]
Seriously, he likes you.
My idiot brother's always
going on at home about
Sato this, and Sato that.
[SATO] But when the election's
over, he will be mine!
You bet I'm gonna date
that prince, and after that,
I'm gonna marry him!
[CROWD cheers]
Are you okay with this?
Uh.
I guess it's fine, as long as
she's cool with announcing it.
I was asking what you
thought about it, you idiot.
What?
[HIKARI] I'm glad the
Break Out's finally over.
It's good to be back
at my real age.
What's with the long face?
Tch!
What did I say to
deserve this, Kanade?
You're hurting me! Cut it out!
I just wanna know
why you're upset! Ow!
[SOICHIRO] So here's a story
for you, a little tale
set right around the time
I entered high school.
Yours truly, Soichiro
Sakurada, king of the realm,
was allowed to attend a normal
school with normal kids,
despite some rather
strenuous objections.
There was one big problem
with this arrangement,
though. I was alone.
I hadn't made a real
connection with anyone,
much less any kind of friend.
Freaks me out.
[SOICHIRO] Is that contempt?
Fear? No, more like dread.
I might as well get used to it.
As long as I'm king,
I'll always be an outsider.
That's just the way it goes.
Of course, the personal maid
doesn't help matters.
Who's gonna come up and
talk to me with her looming
over my shoulder all the time?
Hey, Sowa?
My liege?
I don't think you're
allowed in here.
I didn't realize you were
going to the restroom!
I'm so sorry, I'll wait
outside, Your Majesty!
[SOICHIRO] As both my royal
caretaker and bodyguard,
Sowa is truly something special.
She's always been devoted
to her duties and gladly
placed her trust in me.
But it was hard to
make friends with her
at my heels 24 hours a day.
As if my classmates
weren't terrified enough.
I felt kinda bad about
it, but I ditched her
whenever I got the chance.
In fact, that was the
17th time I'd done it.
You'd think she'd have
caught on by then.
[SOICHIRO] That day, I decided
to check out the roof.
Ah.
[gasps]
[SOICHIRO]
I've never seen her before.
Why's she all the way up here?
[SOICHIRO]
There's a petal on her nose.
Whoa! Who in the heck are you?
[SOICHIRO] Sorry, I didn't
mean to scare you.
I'm just a guy who tried to pick
a flower petal off your face.
[SATSUKI]
Yeah right, like I believe that.
Just admit it, you were trying
to sneak a peek, weren't ya?
No.
I promise I would never do
anything like that
to you, I swear.
Okay. Good!
What, am I not cute enough
for you or something?
[SOICHIRO]
I didn't mean it like that!
Man, girls are confusing.
Well, you're in luck.
'Cause I know just how
you can make it up to me.
[SOICHIRO]
What do you have in mind?
[SATSUKI]
Shopping.
[SOICHIRO] Um. Sure. Wait,
you mean like, right now?
[SATSUKI]
When did you think?
Don't you have classes?
I'm skipping.
It's a good thing I caught you.
I actually have a lot
to pick up today.
[SOICHIRO] My royal superpower
allows me to see emotions.
They usually appear
to me as a colored aura.
But this girl was a mystery--
completely colorless.
Why doesn't she light up
with the same fear
that the others do?
What're you staring at me for?
Or do you gawk at
every girl that way?
No, of course not.
I'm sorry about that.
Why the heck is she
buying so much food?
Is she cooking for
an army, or what?
Sounds good. Nice to
see you with a boy.
He's nothing more
than my packhorse.
Hey, Packhorse,
ain't I seen you before?
I don't think so.
Just one of those faces.
I'll say.
You look just like
every other bozo in town.
[laughs in monotone]
[SATSUKI] The sun's setting.
When did it get so late?
Guess you might as well
come in and join us.
[gasps]
Something wrong?
So this is just the entryway
to your home, right?
No, this is the whole house.
[ALL gasping]
[SATSUKI'S KID BROTHER]
Who is this girl
and what has she
done with my sister?
She would never
bring home a boy!
[SATSUKI]
Shut up, you little twerp.
It's nice to meet you.
You're more than welcome
to join us for dinner,
if you'd like.
They're cooking it up right now.
Thank you very much.
[SATSUKI'S TEEN SISTER]
C'mon, you can tell me!
Is he your boyfriend or what?
[SATSUKI]
Not even a little.
Wow, Mister, you're really tall!
[SOICHIRO]
Hm?
You gotta tell me how
you got like that!
[SOICHIRO]
Curiosity, anticipation.
I've never seen these colors.
Well, you know--
All I did was eat right and get
plenty of sleep growing up.
For real? I could
totally do that!
[ALL]
Thank you for the food!
Do you cook your family
dinner every night?
[SATSUKI] Both our parents
work, so I pick up the slack
whenever they come home late.
That's very impressive.
[SATSUKI] My little sisters
help out with the prep,
so I can't take all the credit.
[SATSUKI'S TEEN SISTER]
She's being modest.
Her specialty is the
simmered taro dish,
so you gotta make
sure you try it.
You've got some talent!
Thanks.
Whoa, I've never seen
your cheeks so red before!
[SATSUKI]
Pipe down and eat your rice!
The omelette you made
is really good, too!
[SATSUKI]
Glad you like it.
Uh-oh, you've got food on your
cheek, I'll get it for you.
Some more rice, please!
There are lots of other
yummy foods in the world,
y'know! Here try this!
[SATSUKI'S KID BROTHER]
You know I hate carrots!
[SATSUKI'S TEEN BROTHER]
Open wide and say "ah."
[SOICHIRO chuckles]
[SATSUKI] Wait a sec.
Did you call your home
to let them know where you are?
Yeah. At least,
I tried to call Sowa.
Who?
[SOICHIRO] She's my guardian.
I know, weird, right?
My mom passed away
when I was a little kid
and my dad died
a few years back.
So now she sort of
takes care of me.
I miss them a lot, but
I've got plenty of people
looking out for me,
so I never feel alone.
Still. I don't have any
siblings of my own.
Let's play a card game!
[SOICHIRO] They might get on
your nerves, but I kinda feel
like I've missed out, you know?
I can't do it alone!
[SATSUKI'S TEEN BROTHER]
I've got my own!
[SATSUKI'S KID SISTER]
I can help you out!
[SOICHIRO] It must be
wonderful to have a family.
[SATSUKI'S KID SISTER]
Yay!
[SATSUKI]
Yeah, it is.
Thank you for having me.
Whatever.
[SOICHIRO]
By the way. Do you always nap
on the roof during lunch?
Well, I wouldn't say always.
It's better when it's sunny.
Hey!
You better not steal
my secret nap spot!
I wouldn't dream of it.
Oh, that reminds me,
I never introduced myself.
I'm Satsuki Shinonome,
second year.
[gasps] Oh, I'm
just a first year.
You can call me Soichiro--
[SATSUKI]
You're Sakurada, right?
[gasps]
Well, it was nice having
you over for dinner,
"Your Majesty."
[gasps] You knew
this whole time?
I'll see you at school tomorrow.
[SOWA whimpering]
Where have you been,
Your Majesty?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
You're too kind.
Some guardian I am.
Who keeps watch outside
a bathroom for hours
before realizing you
aren't in there anymore?
My lord.
I wasn't even able to
ensure you had a healthy
and nutritious dinner tonight!
[SOICHIRO]
Tell me something, Sowa.
Do you think tomorrow
will be sunny?
[gasps] I'll find out
the forecast for you
right this moment!
[HIKARI]
Whoa! Have you seen this one?
Daddy and Shu could be twins!
Your old man was
a handsome king!
Despite what certain
shopkeepers said!
That's right.
You'd already been sitting
on the throne for a few years
by the time you were Shu's age.
He's a lazy king!
Didn't I ask you to
tidy up before dinner?
My mistake. I'm sorry, honey.
Guess your title doesn't
count for much with Mom.
[laughs] My crown
doesn't make me
any less of a normal person.
Matter of fact, normal happiness
beats a crown any day.
Your mom's the one
who taught me that.
Hey, Dad.
[SOICHIRO]
Hm?
You're right.
You warned us being a
member of the royal family
would never be easy, 'cause
we're always in the public eye.
Leaving the house
becomes a production.
And we're expected to smile
and wave at the crowds
who follow us around.
It can be tough.
So, were you scared?
Knowing you would ask
Mom to live that way?
To put up with so much.
[SOICHIRO]
Not for a moment.
She was the driving
force when it came to
living in the public eye.
Her courage made me brave.
She'd warn me
whenever people
were watching us.
Then she'd force me
to smile and wave.
A lesson I'm glad I learned.
I wouldn't be the
king I am today
if it weren't for your mother.
The only reason I smile
and laugh the way I do
is because she taught me how.
And I'll spend the
rest of my life
trying to repay her for that.
That's why there's nothing
more important to me
as a man and a king, than
keeping my family happy.
Thank you, Dad.
[SATO] Why would Shu
ask me to the roof?
Is it about my overdramatic
speech at the café?
Did I ruin everything?
[SHU]
Hey!
Would you mind coming up here?
[SHU]
Sato.
[SATO]
Yeah?!
Let's talk.
I never thought for one second
that I would actually
want to be king.
Huh?
It just didn't matter to me.
Probably because I've
watched Kanade work so hard
in her campaigning to wear
the crown for my sake.
Uh. What are we talking about?
I've been thinking about it,
and I've decided to follow
in my father's footsteps.
[SATO] He does wanna
end things with me!
He's going for the crown and
he thinks I'll hold him back!
But how can he break up with me
when we aren't even
officially going out?
I mean, we talked about it--
[SHU] There's something
I need to tell you!
[SATO gasps]
What the--?
Whoa, where did you take us?
I thought for sure the
Break Out was over by now.
[SATO]
He's gonna break up with me
and then leave me in
this frigid wasteland!
Sato!
Would you please
just listen to me?
It's done, okay? We're
over. Now let me go!
[gasps]
[SATO] I'll do my best
to try and forget about
my feelings for you.
When we were little,
I liked you so much.
And I'm happy we had
a chance to try.
We talked and you
walked me home.
It was like a dream come true.
But it wasn't meant to be.
I'm not worthy of
a prince's love.
I'd keep you from doing
incredible things.
I couldn't live with
myself if I held you back!
I'm sorry.
Guess I was wrong.
I was worried that
you couldn't handle
the glare of the spotlight.
[SATO]
Huh?
[SHU] But you stood up in
front of a crowd of strangers
and told them all
how you feel about me,
so now I have to know--
Know what? Please.
If I do win this election,
will you stay with me?
[SATO gasps]
[SHU]
Please?
I told you I'd share my
feelings with you someday.
I like you, too, Hana.
[SATO]
I'm so happy.
Oh, Shu.
I'm freezing.
[yelps]
Hana! Snap out of it!
[SHU] I'm Shu, the
eldest Sakurada son.
[SATSUKI] My Shu is the
spitting image of his dad
at his age and shares
his sense of wonder,
and the way he sees the world!
[SHU]
Well, he is my father.
[SATSUKI] Plus, he's got
an adorable girlfriend,
who cares for him very much!
You two are so cute!
[SATSUKI] If Shu is elected
your king, he'll rule
with wisdom and pride,
delegating what he can
so he can focus
on the big issues!
Go ahead and tell them your
campaign slogan, sweetie.
[SHU] It's simple:
"I'm going to make our country
a bright and peaceful place."
The election's coming up soon.
I'll do all I can
earn your votes!