[NEWSCASTER 1B]
In other news, we've received
the latest poll results
for the royal election.
On top is fan favorite:
Princess Aoi.
Meanwhile, Princesses Kanade
and Akane are neck-n-neck
in their battle
for the second place spot.
Princess Aoi's
still got my vote,
that's for sure.
What about you, Sacchy?
Who's your vote going to?
[SACCHY]
It doesn't matter who wins.
Nothing's gonna change
after the election anyway.
It's gotta matter a little.
I never liked royalty.
They don't have to work
for anything they get
and they live free without
a care for the future.
They get to dance through
life on free royal passes.
They wouldn't know real
hardship if it bit them!
Oh...
[SACCHY]
I've worked hard, but some royal
could swoop in and replace me.
In fact, they could
probably become a top idol
without much effort at all!
Uh...
[SACCHY]
It's not like I'm jealous
or anything crazy like that!
No, of course you're
not. Not at all.
[AKANE groans] I've watched
this concert a million times
and it still makes
my heart soar!
You rock, Sacchy!
[AKANE] I wanna meet her!
No, I need to meet her!
Then go to the show.
[AKANE]
No, I mean really meet her!
Like talk to her and become
her best friend, y'know?
It's not like you
need permission.
You are royalty.
[AKANE] But it can't
be okay for me to use
my position for personal gain.
Although, we are talking
about meeting the Sacchy!
I don't think that
makes it okay.
[AKANE]
Yeah, you're right.
[MATSUOKA]
Here's my plan for your career.
As we get close to the election,
I want to reveal your identity.
Laito's become a huge
sensation and the fans
absolutely adore her energy!
She's not a one-hit-wonder!
If we went ahead and revealed
your true identity now,
think of the impact!
Hikari-mania would
sweep the polls!
If Laito's fan base
and Hikari's supporters
band together, they could
take you all the way
to the royal palace!
Then you'd be in a position
to make some real change!
So after this next concert,
Laito Sakurapa will retire
and the royal idol,
Hikari Sakurada will--
Uh. Are you even
listening to me, Laito?
Huh? Yeah.
Is something wrong?
You know I'm here if you ever
need to talk about anything.
[HIKARI]
It's this dumb hangnail.
Would it kill you
to pay attention
when we're talking
about important things?
[SACCHY]
I don't know why,
but my work as
an idol has seemed
so much more fulfilling lately.
[SACCHY] I've pushed
so hard to get this far
and I'm still giving it my all.
I'm getting better by the day.
Before, I always felt like
I was just going through
the motions when I performed.
But now, I'm loving
every minute of it.
[SACCHY] I think it's
all because of Laito.
[MATSUOKA]
Then it's decided.
Laito's gonna retire
after her next show.
[SACCHY]
What? She's gonna leave?
No. It's not possible!
She's at the top of her
career! Maybe not even!
She could probably rise
higher if she wanted!
What in the world could
make her want to quit now?
I guess if there was some
kind of trouble at home,
she'd have to leave her
music career behind.
Come to think of it, she's
never talks about her family.
Or anything outside
of work. I wonder why.
[MS. YAMAMOTO]
Hey there.
You were deep in thought.
Everything good?
Oh, yeah, everything's great.
[MATSUOKA] Laito's
popularity has skyrocketed
since her debut and she's
gaining a strong fan base.
Your collaboration
was a great success.
And your support
has meant a lot.
Thanks very much, Sacchy.
And, though you may not
be a permanent duo,
the fans did love seeing
you sing side-by-side.
Oh, yeah, they did!
So whaddya say we do it again?
Who's up for a Search
Light reunion show?
[HIKARI, SACCHY]
Mm...
[MATSUOKA]
Uh... So this concert.
Let's pull together
and make it special.
Sachiko. I want you
to take the lead.
[SACCHY]
I can't believe she's leaving.
Let's get out there and give 'em
one heck of a show.
All right then.
Make sure to take
good care of yourselves.
No getting sick now.
--[SACCHY] Of course.
--[HIKARI] Yes, sir.
[SACCHY]
They're not gonna say a word.
She's going to leave
and never come back.
Come on, that's enough! What
am I worrying about, anyway?
I got all the way here on my own
and survived fine
before she showed up.
I bet she has perfectly
good reasons to leave.
I'll just go back
to being alone.
[MATSUOKA]
What?! How'd you get the flu?!
[MS. YAMAMOTO]
I'm sorry, Mr. Matsuoka.
I have no idea how it happened.
Don't come in to work!
Even if you feel better,
you understand?
We can't risk an epidemic,
not with the concert so close!
[MS. YAMAMOTO]
Okay.
I can't believe poor
Ms. Yamamoto caught the flu.
Yeah.
And on top of that, we're now
short staffed for the concert.
We need some back up, quick.
Ah! Actually, I know
someone who would be
willing to work hard
for basically no pay!
Oh, really, who?
[MATSUOKA] We have a new
assistant joining us.
She'll be filling in for
Ms. Yamamoto until she recovers.
Meet Lady Akagi.
[MATSUOKA, HIKARI
laugh nervously]
[SACCHY]
The heck?
You can just call me Akagi.
I'm so grateful for the
opportunity to help out.
Lemme know if there's
anything you need.
Okay. Well, I'm excited
to work with you.
[SACCHY]
Wow, she's blushing like crazy.
Maybe this is her first job?
[AKANE] Wait, I get to
be Sacchy's assistant?
You would be our assistant!
I'm gonna hug her so
close and never let go!
Don't you even think about it!
After I transform you
with my powers,
we'll need a good disguise
so no one will recognize you.
You don't have to
worry about a thing!
I've got my pair of Jamming
Glasses, they'll do the trick.
[HIKARI] Um, I don't think
that those are gonna help.
Uh?
I am truly honored to
meet you, Your Highness.
Allow me to apologize for any
trouble we may have caused.
If you're gonna call
her "Your Highness,"
then why bother with a disguise?
[MATSUOKA] I must be polite
in front of the princess.
Thank you, but there's
no need for all of that.
Honestly, I'd rather you
just be yourself around me.
[gasps] My, what a
gracious gesture.
You're so humble. I'll do
anything I can to help.
[HIKARI]
Is he blushing?
He's never fawned
over me like that!
[music playing]
[AKANE] Hikari practices
for hours on end.
I never knew she had it in her.
[HIKARI] Everyone's gonna
know who I really am.
What'll they think of me
when I tell the truth?
And what about Laito?
[SACCHY] You're a little
off on that last part.
[gasps] Oh. I'm sorry.
Gotta make it right.
Or you'll regret it at the show.
[gasps] Yeah, guess so.
[gasps]
I'm gonna run to
the store real quick.
I'd be happy to go for you!
[SACCHY]
Thanks, but I got it.
I could really use
some fresh air.
[AKANE]
Okay. Be safe.
Do you think maybe she's
nervous about the show?
No, she just wants
everything to be perfect.
[SACCHY gasps]
I totally forgot my purse.
[SACCHY sighs]
Now what? This is
driving me crazy.
[sighs]
If it's gonna be
her final concert,
I can't let her down.
[MATSUOKA]
Aren't you and Sachiko supposed
to rehearse tonight?
Yeah, she just ran to the store.
I see. This is a big
concert for you two.
You ready for the world to
know your real identity?
Your fans are gonna
be so blown away!
I wanted to talk to you.
Huh?
It's about this "revealing
my identity" thing.
[MATSUOKA] What? You don't
want to do the reveal now?
I've been thinking about
why I became an idol.
At first, I was just
looking for an easy way
to campaign, y'know?
But now, it's different.
Being an idol has become
a special part of my life.
And I think that's because
this is the first time
I've ever had to work
for something on my own.
The first time. Huh.
When I see my fans cheering,
and I know it's because
of me, it's like...
...I finally understand how
much strength I have inside.
In the end,
the good I've done as
an idol belongs to Laito
and her crowds more than to me.
And it's not right to use
that for my own gain.
I love my fans.
And I'm so grateful
for their support.
Performing as Laito
is how I pay them back.
Okay then.
I hope your fans know how
lucky they are to have you.
[HIKARI] I can't tell you
how much this means to me.
But--
I still feel like I'm lying
to the entire agency.
Do you think I should tell them?
Everyone's been so
supportive of me.
[MATSUOKA]
That's a big decision to make.
Why don't you take some
time to think it over?
[HIKARI]
Okay.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Sure.
Okay, so...
If you keep up a lie
for a long time,
does it ever become the truth?
[gasps] Yes, it's possible,
but in the end,
it depends on who you're
lying to. You know?
Sorta.
If you're lying to yourself,
it'll never be true.
But what's worse than
that, it'll eventually
hurt the ones you love.
[MATSUOKA]
All right, ladies.
We've hit a few bumps on
the road, but we've made it!
Now it's time to get on that
stage and sing your hearts out!
[HIKARI, SACCHY]
Let's do it.
[AKANE]
Aw man, the poor things must be
a bundle of nerves right now.
Okay, I gotta do what I
can to change the mood!
Let's get it rockin', you two!
When the curtain falls,
katsu bowls are on me!
[SACCHY]
That's too much food for me.
[HIKARI]
I'm more of a ramen girl.
Uh-- Eh-heh...
[SACCHY]
So, Laito's really a princess.
Has she been "playing idol"
as a campaign publicity stunt?
Maybe she only got this
far because her family
was pulling some strings
in the background.
But I've seen her work so hard.
[SACCHY]
At least she's not really
going to retire after this.
We can still perform
together and--
[gasps]
[SACCHY] What am I even
thinking? Focus, Sachiko!
[SACCHY] Gotta make it right.
Or you'll regret it at the show.
Five minutes. You okay?
[HIKARI]
Yup!
You'll never catch an idol
without her smile on!
I'm gonna go out there
and rock this thing!
[SACCHY gasps]
[AKANE giggles]
Yeah, you will!
[HIKARI]
Time to make it happen!
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[HIKARI]
I have to tell her the truth.
Just say the words, be brave
or you'll regret it.
Hey, Sacchy.
There's something
I need to tell you.
We're at places.
Can you wait till
after the show?
I can't.
Well, you may have to.
If I don't tell you this now,
I won't be able to
perform at my best.
I've been keeping
a secret from you.
I wasn't sure if I should
say, but we're a team,
so it's only fair that you know.
I don't want to lie, Sacchy.
I've done enough of that.
My real name is Hikari
Sakurada. The royal princess.
I know. Why did you
hide it until now?
Because I was scared.
I was worried you wouldn't
take me seriously anymore
if you knew I was royalty.
But being an idol
means everything to me
and I'm willing to
work crazy hard
so I can get as good as you!
Ow, that hurt!
Stop! Now I got something
to tell you, Princess!
I can tell when my friend
is giving it her all!
Do you think I care what
family you come from?
They aren't the ones
who spent endless hours
rehearsing with me.
You may be "Hikari"
whenever you're at home,
but you'll always
be Laito to me, got it?
[SACCHY]
Now, let's get out there.
This is our moment to shine.
[HIKARI]
Yeah!
[AKANE] We were born
and raised as royalty.
And I'd always thought that
meant staying inside the lines,
and thinking twice
before I acted.
Life wasn't about
what I wanted to do,
but what I was supposed to do.
[AKANE] But when my little
sister's on that stage,
I barely recognize her.
That silly, irresponsible
girl has suddenly grown up
before my eyes. She's doing
something that matters to her!
She found a song, and she's
gonna sing her heart out.
And never worry if
it's appropriate or not
for a princess. I've
never been more proud.
And I'll admit,
maybe a little jealous.
[KANADE]
It was great to meet you two.
And you as well,
Princess, thank you.
Nice meeting you. I hope
you win the election!
[KANADE]
Aw, thanks! Have a good day!
And that's how you win 'em over
on the campaign trail!
[KANADE] I've got a long
list, where do I start?
Vegetables are probably
the way to go,
even if I have to
lug them around,
then the meat won't spoil.
Okay then.
Tomorrow looks like it's gonna
be a big day of campaigning.
Two important speeches
before noon.
Close the day with
handshakes and a talk show.
I'm not that crazy about
doing a talk show.
If you're gonna do this,
you'll do it right.
Do you wanna win
the crown or not?
[SHU]
Okay, okay.
But what I need right now
is for you to go over
the speech I wrote you
and make sure it's okay.
I'm so lucky to have you.
[BUTCHER 10A] Very sorry
to keep you waiting, Miss.
[gasps]
What can I get for ya?
Uh, I'm looking for
Chuck Eye Roll
if you have it in the shop.
[BUTCHER 10A]
Coming right up.
[sighs]
[GIRL 10B]
Hey, Mommy?
Can we go to the park
when we're done shopping?
Pretty please?
Sorry, sweetheart, but Mommy's
gotta get dinner ready.
We promised to help
set the table, remember?
You wouldn't wanna eat
without a napkin, would ya?
[GIRL 10B]
But I'm not ready to go home.
I wanna play some more!
[BOY 10A]
Twist my arm, why dontcha?
Tell you what, when we get
home, I'll read you a book.
[GIRL 10B]
You mean it?
[KANADE gasps]
[KANADE]
But, what happened?
No!
[DOCTOR 10A] Both children have
come through the worst now.
I suspect that Princess Akane
is going to experience
some memory loss, but she's
physically unharmed.
[SOICHIRO]
Thank goodness.
[DOCTOR 10A]
As for Prince Shu, however,
his injuries were more severe.
I doubt it'll affect his
day-to-day activities,
but his leg's motor functions
will never be the same.
I am sorry, my liege.
Modern medicine can
do no more than this.
[SOICHIRO] All of my children
are alive and safe.
A father can't ask
for anything else.
[DOCTOR 10A] There's one thing
to note about Princess Kanade.
Her creations are
limited only by money.
If she has the funds,
she can materialize
almost anything she wants.
Although...
It appears that if she tries
to conjure up something
outside her means, like
she did at the park,
then her other creations will
be consumed as collateral.
[SOICHIRO]
I don't understand.
[DOCTOR 10A] Well, in this
instance, when she tried to make
the staircase, the castle's
foundation was appropriated.
[sobs]
[KANADE] That fateful day,
Shu lost something precious.
And in the end, so did I.
[KANADE] My brother's dream
of playing soccer was gone.
But maybe I can bring it back.
If I win this election,
I just might.
[BUTCHER 10A] Is there anything
else I can get for ya?
Prince Shu!
How about a few
of those sausages?
[BUTCHER 10A]
Right away!
[SHU] I can tell there's
something on your mind.
What, I can't just
stand here and think?
Weren't you spending
the day with Sato?
I didn't want her to
have to walk in the rain.
So I just teleported her home.
Geez, you're dumb.
What?
Rainy days're romantic, moron!
It's the perfect weather
to walk a girl home!
Wait, that's how it works?
[sighs] Man, you're hopeless.
You want me to carry that stuff?
I could just teleport
us back home, you know.
Yeah, but I don't mind walking.
It gives me the chance
to connect with citizens
and do a little campaigning.
You are all about the votes.
You got a problem with that?
Hey, Kanade?
Yeah?
I really hope you're not
trying to become king
just so you can use the national
budget in some crazy attempt
to fix my legs, or anything
like that nonsense.
If you'd like to
know my opinion,
I'd rather you not
do that, actually.
Why's it matter?
Because I care about you.
I'd never want you
to waste your life
on something silly like that.
And besides, I may not be
able to sprint anymore,
but teleporting is
much more fun, anyway.
And, I'm not really
the bragging type,
but I'm doing pretty
great life-wise,
if you catch my drift.
I catch it just fine, thanks.
Whenever you talk about
Sato, you're smiling.
Huh?
Hint, hint, maybe you should
be with your girlfriend
instead of me.
But you're the one I'm
trying to get a smile outta.
Please, I smile plenty.
I dunno, that answer
didn't sound too upbeat.
Look, I'm your twin, I know what
you're thinking at all times.
Of course, how could I forget?
What, you doubt me?
Yeah, that's the word,
'cause I know I've got
no clue what's going on inside
that thick skull of yours!
I know you're thinking
about the accident.
And I want you to let it go!
[KANADE] Well, that's never
gonna happen, okay?
[gasps]
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to yell like that.
I'm just frustrated
because I want
to make it up to you somehow.
Thing is,
I don't think I'll ever
really be able to do that
because I owe you so much.
That's not true.
But I'm gonna keep trying.
It's the least I can do.
C'mon, don't be ridiculous,
you don't owe me anything, sis.
I do!
Nuh-uh. That's not how
it works with your family.
[gasps]
As a matter of fact.
Even back when it happened,
I didn't hold it against you.
So leave the past in the past.
No way. I can't accept
that and just move on!
That's cool. You don't
have to accept it.
But I'm pretty sure that you do
have to listen to
your big brother.
[gasps] What the heck's
wrong with you?
You've never pulled
rank on me before.
Don't get all
"big brother" on me now.
C'mon, lil' sis.
I've been around the block
a few times, so I know best.
You're only older than me
by like 30 minutes, you jerk!
Thirty minutes or 30 seconds.
It still makes me
older than you.
I'm not gonna stand
here and listen to you
mock me like this!
Hey, calm down, you don't
wanna fight out here.
I mean, I'd hate for your
image to suffer in the polls
because of a sibling squabble.
Would you just shut up?
[panting]
[KANADE grunting]
Kana, come back!
[gasps]
[KANADE gasps]
[SHU]
Wow.
Got out right in the
nick of time, huh?
Are you all right, Kana?
[KANADE]
Yeah. I'm okay.
[SHU]
Good.
I don't know what I'd do if
anything ever happened to you.
[KANADE gasps]
I'm so happy that you're safe.
How can you be so reckless?
[SHU]
Hm?
You put yourself in danger.
What would you do if these
stupid risks got you hurt again?
And why in the world
are you always like this?
Even after everything
you've been through,
you still act like a hero!
Aw, c'mon.
[gasps]
Any brother worth his
salt would rather die
than let something happen
to his little sister.
Don't count on me
stopping anytime soon.
It's not fair for you to be
responsible for everyone!
Oh, yeah, totally unfair.
You got a problem with that?
[gasps]
No matter what happens to me,
I will always protect you.
And I know you're gonna
hate it when I do.
But there's no chance I'll
stop riding to your rescue.
That's the sort of thing
big brothers do.
That said.
How about you quit
fighting it and just let me
protect you when need be?
Brothers and sisters don't
"owe" each other anything.
If I wanna spoil you
rotten, then let me.
Because there's nothing
I love more in the world.
Shu...
[KANADE sobbing]
[KANADE]
Okay, I'm not crying anymore.
You can put me down!
C'mon, this is
getting embarrassing.
What, you think you're too
old for a piggyback ride?
Yeah.
Here's the thing.
I know I could teleport
you home, but I chose
to give you a
piggyback ride because
I wanted to prove a point.
[gasps] Yeah, yeah, I get it,
you're like super
strong or whatever.
The point is, I don't
have to carry you.
I'm doing it 'cause I want to.
Don't try to become
king for my sake,
'cause that's not the right
reason. You understand?
I, Kanade Sakurada,
hereby promise
I won't win the crown for you.
Great!
That would be wrong.
I'm gonna win it
because I want to!
And then I'll rule this
land as a terrifying
tyrant and be feared
as the overlord!
I will conquer this realm
with an iron fist!
What?
Believe me.
I'm gonna sit on
the throne someday!
[HARUKA] Hello, I'm
Haruka, the second son.
[SATSUKI] Haru's a kind boy
who works tirelessly
behind the curtain to
keep his family happy.
I know he loves us very much.
[HARUKA]
True.
I'd rather be at home
than hunting for votes.
[SATSUKI] If he is elected
your king, this country
will become full of polite,
considerate citizens,
just like him.
Tell them your
campaign slogan, honey.
[HARUKA] I don't really have
one, but I do have a ruler
I look up to! He wasn't a king,
but Prime Minister Gajah Mada
of the Majapahit
Empire's my favorite.
Please make sure
to get out and vote
for whomever you think
is best for the job!