[MISAKI]
Winning!
[AOI]
We hit the jackpot.
[chuckles]
[HARUKA]
Hi there. I'm Haruka Sakurada.
I'm 14 years old and second son
of the Sakurada Royal Family.
I have eight siblings.
Four older sisters
and an older brother,
plus two younger sisters
and a younger brother.
And we all have special powers.
Yeah. Life is interesting.
[AKANE] I didn't know dad bought
a private beach for us to use.
He wanted to make sure
we could all relax
in total privacy
on our vacation.
So there's no cameras either.
[AKANE] There's nothing
but ocean out there.
Your Transporter must go
even further than I thought.
It's been a while since
all of us got out like this.
[HIKARI]
Hey!
Wanna play "split
the watermelon"?
[AKANE]
You bet!
[HIKARI] It was my idea
so I'm should go first!
[SHIORI]
Split it? Won't that hurt?
[TERU] Don't worry,
Shiori, I'll make it quick!
[HARUKA] Eight percent for Teru.
Two percent for Hikari.
Five percent for Misaki.
Shu's at one percent.
Looks like Akane's around
ten. Aoi's also at one.
And Shiori's rockin' 80%.
This is Lots of Next.
It's my special power.
[KANADE]
What numbers are you crunching?
Who will split the melon first.
Huh?
[HARUKA]
Kanade has a 50% shot, huh?
[gasps]
[KANADE]
Shiori's really that high?
[HARUKA]
Yup.
Well, it's just a chance,
not an absolute,
so I guess we'll
see what happens.
[yelling]
[TERU]
Oh, you dodged me, huh? Not bad.
But let's see you
survive my grand slam!
Nice.
I can't even split
a stupid watermelon?
If this crap keeps up, there's
no way I'll become a real man!
Geez. Chill, Teru.
It's just a game.
[HIKARI]
Gotcha!
Whoopsy-daisy.
Looks like I missed it!
Tone down the idol act. You
don't have an audience out here.
Mr. Matsuoka said I should
practice every waking moment.
Next.
[yells]
That... was close.
Show it whose boss, Akane!
[AKANE]
Uh, sure!
[HIKARI]
It's right in front of you!
She's lying! It's to your right!
[AKANE]
Which way is right again?
Swing now and you've got it!
Aw! She went right passed it!
To your left now!
This is way too confusing.
Is it over here?
Yes!
[grunts]
Darn it! You were so close!
[SHU] This is even
harder than it looks.
[SHIORI]
You can do it, Big Sister.
So close and yet so far.
Oh. I see what's going on.
[KANADE] The two of them missed
on purpose so Shiori could win.
Sorry, short stuff.
I love you, but I can't let
Haruka's prediction come true.
[HARUKA] She's getting serious
about this. I can feel it.
In front of you!
It's to the right!
[HIKARI]
No, keep going forward!
[TERU]
Go to the right!
[HARUKA] Kanade's not even
listening to the others.
She has a purpose.
Not to mention a 50-50 shot
at splitting the melon first.
This could be really bad.
Shiori's supposed
to be the winner.
She has the highest
chance of all!
Oh no. Her distance
and angle are perfect!
Here comes the moment of truth.
[yells]
[KANADE]
No way.
[HARUKA]
Yes.
You're tougher than you
look, I'll give you that.
It's your turn, Shiori.
You got this.
If you can't do it,
we'll start over.
[TERU]
It's dead ahead.
C'mon, give it a good whack!
[AKANE] That's it!
Keep going straight ahead!
[MISAKI]
You can do it!
[HARUKA]
She's got this in the bag.
Then again,
Kanade gave it her all and
the melon didn't even crack.
Is Shiori strong
enough to split it?
No, don't go there.
I need to believe in my power!
[WATERMELON]
Halt, villain!
Thou shalt not reach my juicy
center without a fight, knave!
Try if thou darest!
Have at thee!
[SHIORI] I don't wanna
hit you, Mr. Watermelon.
[WATERMELON] Uh! Doth this mean
thou feel-eth pity for me?
Truly, child?
[SHIORI] I do. It's not nice
to hurt someone. I hate it.
Swing, Shiori!
It's right where you want it!
[SHIORI]
I can't. I don't want to.
[WATERMELON]
Tis fine, little one.
Thou art the first soul
who hath ever shown me
true kindness and respect.
For that, I am deeply grateful.
Now, giveth me a good thunk!
[SHIORI]
I can't.
[WATERMELON]
Ye must.
For there is no other way
to reach my deliciousness.
[SHIORI]
Mr. Watermelon.
[WATERMELON]
Farewell. I am glad that we met.
[HARUKA]
No!
Looks like we're starting over.
She did it!
[HARUKA]
Eat it!
[AKANE]
Split perfectly?
I'm sorry.
[WATERMELON]
Don't be!
For I do not regret a single
slice of life. Huzzah!
[HIKARI] Akane! Let's play
some more volleyball!
'Kay!
You can run around all you like,
but make sure you don't
go past the fence line.
It's for your safety.
Is there some kinda animal
out there, or something?
[SHU] No. Just don't
go past it, all right?
[MISAKI]
Hey! Who were you passing to?
Akane, go get it!
[AKANE]
You bet!
Leave it to me and my
patented super jump!
Hey! What did I just tell you?
It's going faster
than I thought.
[SHU] No, Akane! Stop!
Don't go past the fence!
It's okay, there's nothing!
[HARUKA]
Nailed it.
Whoa. What is this?
[SHU] I was hoping
you wouldn't find out.
[AKANE]
Huh?
[SHU] We're not actually
on a tropical island.
It's a prefabricated set
in the middle of an empty lot.
Not cool!
[SHU]
Did you guys honestly think
the guards would let us
get that far out of sight?
You big dumb jerk!
If you're going to trick us, at
least put some effort into it!
You know you messed up
when Hikari gets angry,
and to be honest with you,
I'm right there with her.
[SHU]
Don't worry. It's not all fake.
The sand and water are real.
Oh, that's okay then.
He's only saying that
to make you feel better!
[AKANE] You didn't have to
go to all this trouble, Shu.
Really. I'm not shy
when I'm having fun.
[SHU]
Oh, my bad.
I was afraid you might
be stressed out.
Nah. But you're sweet.
[thudding]
[MISAKI] Wow, this is
pretty sturdy stuff.
[HIKARI] Don't they use
these things on game shows?
[TERU]
It looks so real.
Yeah, it felt real, too.
[TERU]
Yeah.
[MISAKI gasps]
[AKANE]
Huh?
[SHU]
Uhh...
[ONLOOKERS mummbling, gasping]
[screaming]
[AKANE screaming]
I wish Shu would think
things through sometimes.
[HARUKA]
What? No way!
[AKANE]
Uh?
[HARUKA]
Wow. There's this many already?
Ugh. There're even more here.
[HARUKA]
I better get started.
[gasps]
[HARUKA] Misaki, I told
you to knock before--
[BOTH screaming]
Akane, how long were you there?
Uh. A couple of seconds, maybe?
[HARUKA]
Tell me.
[AKANE]
Huh?
[HARUKA]
Did you see?
Um. See what?
[HARUKA]
You did!
Of course she'd walk in now.
Darn it! What should I tell her?
I'm sorry, Haruka.
I guess you're busy, huh?
Lots of pictures to
look at. Maybe I--
Back up. Did you even knock?
You know what I think of people
who don't respect
other's privacy.
I forgot!
[HARUKA]
Got her!
Hey, are you trying to trick me?
[HARUKA]
Fine. I'll tell you.
'Kay.
That wasn't you.
It was your doppelgänger.
I've been tracking it
down so I can slay it.
[AKANE]
Like I'd believe that crap!
Why won't he tell
me the truth?
I mean, it was only a picture,
right? What is he hiding?
[HARUKA]
Oh, Akane.
[AKANE]
Stop it, Haruka!
That's wrong on so many levels!
We're brother and sister.
And, even if we weren't, this
would still be a problem.
I mean, it's not that I
don't like you or anything,
but it's all so sudden.
What would our family think?
What would the country think?
It's not like that.
No reading my mind
without permission!
Now you respect privacy?
Relax. I was just watching
your body language.
Okay, out with it. Is there
a reason you can't tell me?
Does anyone else
know about this?
[HARUKA]
Yes to both, actually.
Hey, Misaki, guess what?
[HARUKA]
Okay, okay! Hold on!
Look, nobody else
knows, all right?
I can't tell anyone,
no matter who they are.
Trust me, it's nothing you
need to worry about at all.
In fact, if you could forget
this ever happened,
that would be great.
Would you please put that away?
[HARUKA]
If Misaki finds out,
she'll blab about
it to everybody!
Should I go ahead and spill it?
No, that would defeat
the purpose entirely.
Your time's up.
[HARUKA]
Let me say one more thing!
Give me all the juicy details!
[HARUKA screaming]
If you buy me some
pudding from the shop
next to the train station,
I'll take you to any
amusement park you want!
For real?
Back in a flash!
[HARUKA]
Okay, fine, I'll tell you.
You're almost never online,
so I figured you didn't
know about this.
There are all kinds
of fan websites
dedicated to our family.
I've been flagging all
of the uploaded pictures
of you for deletion, but it's
hard to keep up sometimes.
And that means?
[HARUKA]
This'll take a while.
You know what a website is?
Well, fan sites are made
to discuss specific topics.
In this case, the
topic is our family,
and it's loaded
with pictures of us.
People share the pics
and videos they like
and chat about all
of us ad nauseam.
It's considered entertainment,
so it's perfectly legal.
But I know how embarrassed
you get, so I kept it from you
and got rid of everything
that I could find.
[AKANE]
What are they saying about me?
[HARUKA]
Um, nothing really.
"She's adorable" or
"I like how shy she is"
or "I didn't see it."
"I didn't see it"?
What do they--?
[screaming]
[HARUKA] If you didn't
keep losing your skirt,
this wouldn't happen.
[AKANE] I'm never leaving the
house again! Stupid internet!
[HARUKA] Welcome back.
I'm glad you're still with me.
Now, shall we continue?
Next, I'll be talking about
my twin sister, Misaki.
Okay. What's my
schedule for today?
Baseball club, soccer club,
cooking club, tea ceremony club,
subbing in for the drama club,
and modeling for the art club.
[sighs]
They never take a break,
do they? Even in summer.
[MISAKI]
Time to work!
[CLONES]
Got it!
[HARUKA]
This is Misaki's special power.
It's called All for One.
It allows her to create up
to seven clones of herself.
[MISAKI] All right.
What do I have lined up?
Interview for the school
newspaper's next column piece.
"The Sakarada Family's
Six Royal Beauties."
Hmm.
I'm so sorry, Misaki,
but I said I would lend a hand
to the student council today.
You've handled these before.
Why fix what isn't broken?
I can't just sit in front of
strangers and talk about myself!
Please take care of
this for me, Misaki!
[sighs]
No choice. Let's do this thing.
Buh-bye!
I can't forgive you, Cinderella.
Bam!
[OPPONENT]
Lost again.
[BUBU]
Yummy noms.
I hope you enjoy it.
[RAIO]
'Scuse me while I rock this!
[MISAKI] Aoi and Kanade
are great at home.
They're like the perfect older
sisters. Strong and reliable.
Akane is energetic and
tons of fun to be around.
She really sets the mood.
[INTERVIEWER]
Wonderful.
Now, your older sisters
are pretty popular.
What do you think sets you
apart from the three of them?
[INARI]
Misaki!
[CLONES]
I finished helping the club!
Great job, guys.
[HARUKA] Each clone
represents a different part
of Misaki's personality.
They also have their
own special talents,
which make them good additions
to the various clubs at school.
[CLONES chattering]
[INTERVIEWER]
Hey!
What a snore fest.
Why don't you try asking
some entertaining questions?
Will you give that
back, already?
I can think of at
least a dozen zingers
right off the top of my head.
Like, "What color is
Misaki's underwear?"
You can keep that
stuff to yourself!
Haruka! I'm ready
to go home, are you?
I'm kind of busy.
I'll be here for a bit,
so don't wait up for me.
Yeah, right. There's
no need to be shy.
I know you were waiting
with baited breath.
C'mon, let's get
moving, silly-billy.
You can read with your
fake glasses on at home.
You wouldn't believe
the day I've had.
Misaki! Bubu was
a great help today.
Send her anytime.
We'd love to have her.
'Kay! See ya!
Oh, Misaki. Yuniko was awesome.
She hit a grand slam in
the bottom of the ninth.
Could she play again
with us next week?
Hold on, I'll check.
Yup.
She's totally free to play
whenever you need her.
You can use her all you like.
You're kind of like your
clones' manager, aren't you?
[yelps]
Well, I don't have any special
talents of my own, so, y'know.
[PLAYER C]
Thanks for earlier, Misaki.
Raio's kick is out
of this world.
She was the star
of the game today.
Sure. It's no biggie,
I'm glad she could help out.
[chuckles] You're so modest.
Now that I think of it,
your clones have helped
almost every club in
school, haven't they?
Huh? Yeah. They all
have been pretty busy.
It kinda feels like the only
one with any free time is me.
[PLAYER B] Between your clones
and your older sisters,
I bet it's like being in a
school full of superheroes.
It goes to show how much we can
rely on the Sakurada family.
Yeah, I guess so.
You carry our school
on your shoulders.
It's a good thing you
have eight pairs of them.
[MISAKI chuckles nervously]
[MISAKI]
See you tomorrow.
[HARUKA]
It's not just the school.
The country's future is
also your burden to bear.
[MISAKI]
We're home.
[AKANE]
Oh, welcome back!
Perfect timing!
Mr. Mashima is coming by.
Could you do the interview?
Another one?
Yeah.
Aoi and Kanade aren't home,
and you know how I can get.
Please?
Sure. No problem.
Man, I'm just an
interviewing machine today.
It's like the only thing
I'm good for is yammering on
about how freakin' amazing
my older sisters are.
I'm so sick and tired of being
pushed into these things!
[HARUKA]
Talk about a 180.
Did you drag me here
so you could vent
or was there another reason?
[MISAKI] You're supposed to be
there for me! You're my twin!
[PLAYER C] Between your clones
and your older sisters,
I bet it's like being in a
school full of superheroes.
[INTERVIEWER] Your older
sisters are pretty popular.
What do you think sets
you apart from them?
[PLAYER A] You're kind of like
your clones' manager,
aren't you?
[MISAKI]
My clones are always praised
and everyone wants to
know about my sisters.
I might as well be their
shadow or invisible.
People are so insensitive!
You agree with me,
right, Haruka?
Ugh! Fine, don't listen to me!
Keep your stupid eyes glued
to your stupid books!
[HARUKA]
Yep. People are insensitive.
[MISAKI]
I don't need you for this.
I've got my clones.
They'll be my punching bags.
[HARUKA] She can't be serious.
She's gonna yell at herself?
More ball? I'm game!
No way, there's
too much sweating.
We could play shogi, then!
[RAIO] That's all you
ever want to play.
[MISAKI] Quiet! All of you!
It's my turn to talk!
[CLONES]
Huh?
[MISAKI]
Where the heck is Bubu?
Everyone, sit! I didn't
bring you out to socialize!
I'm gonna vent and
you're gonna listen, okay?
You know, if you had
any kind of pride,
you wouldn't have to resort to
ranting at yourself like this.
It's probably some
first world problem.
It must be nice, huh?
[SHAURA] Come on, let's all
relax and cuddle for a while.
Whoa, would ya quit
being so creepy?
Ugh!
Forget it! I'm done with you.
Do whatever you want.
I don't even care anymore.
Calm down, hun.
I'm sitting, now, so
there's no need to fuss.
Have you been skipping meals?
Want some?
[MISAKI] Shut up! You have no
idea what it's like to be me!
Everyone adores you!
Meanwhile, I'm a useless,
no talent, clone factory!
Huh? The heck are
you talking about?
They were practically
lining up to praise you.
[MISAKI]
No, that's not true!
They were stopping me
to praise all of you!
It's like I'm nothing but
an extra, don't you get it?
[MISAKI cries]
[knocking]
He's here! Thanks for
doing this, it means a lot.
[MISAKI]
I'm not.
Great! Then, I'll
just be in my roo--
[AKANE screams]
You're rebelling now?
[YUNIKO]
I always feel sorry for Akane.
[MISAKI] They're not
interested in me. You go do it.
No way! I can't!
You're much better
at this than me!
Don't worry, it'll be okay.
I'll help you get through
it this time, no problem.
[AKANE]
But--
[SHAURA] Let's go. We don't
want to keep him waiting, do we?
[AKANE]
Hold on!
[MISAKI]
It's no use.
My clones can even handle
interviews better than I can.
I guess I really am their
manager, after all.
Ugh, okay.
I know you're feeling down,
but you'll be fine.
[MISAKI] Sorry. It wasn't
fair to complain.
It's just that everything
about me is below average:
grades, sports, looks, fashion.
I should expect this by now.
But I couldn't help feeling
jealous of you guys
and my sisters. It all
comes easy to you.
It's fine, I don't care anymore.
Besides, it's not like
special people like you
would understand a
regular Joe like me.
[CLONES] Like a normal
person could create
clones of themselves.
I don't get you, Misaki.
You keep saying you feel
like a useless extra...
...but we're all a part of you.
Without you, we
would be nothing.
[HARUKA]
It's okay to be normal.
I mean. I'm surrounded by
weirdness on a daily basis.
But you?
You're the one dose of normal
that I can always count on.
If you suddenly stopped
being yourself...
...I don't know what I'd do.
You're far from being a
useless shadow, okay? In fact--
Misaki! Help!
This one's a disaster! She just
keeps flirting with Mr. Mashima!
You're the only one I can trust!
You know how to socialize,
you're objective about everyone,
and you're not a total perv!
There's no one else
who can do this...
[HARUKA] In fact,
you're perfect as you are.
Haru.
I was having so much fun,
but Akane stopped me.
Do you wanna play?
Why did I think you
could handle this?
You're the worst choice of all!
I don't know why
you're so angry.
I just did what I thought you
would do in the situation.
Yeah, right, you
obviously don't know me!
Fine. I can take it from here.
I swear, you guys are
hopeless without me around.
You're my hero!
[MISAKI] Come here.
Play time's officially over.
Oh, well.
That goes for the
rest of you, too!
[MISAKI]
Darn it, Bubu!
All right, I'll be back.
I knew she'd be okay.
I'm glad I was here to
watch out for her though.
[HARUKA]
Misaki, you missed another one!
Morning.
[HARUKA] Get going!
The others already left!
[HARUKA]
Yep. Life sure is interesting.
[MISAKI] I'm the fourth
daughter, Misaki Sakurada!
[SATSUKI]
Misaki tends to be overshadowed
by her unique siblings.
But she's always been
a wonderfully caring
and considerate young lady.
[MISAKI] You're the only one
who really gets me, Momma!
[SATSUKI] As king, she would
be empathetic to her people,
and would work hard to
take good care of them.
Do you have a campaign
promise, sweetie?
[MISAKI]
I'd allow normal people
to enjoy living in a
normal country, I guess.
By the way, the king
I look up to most
is Justinian the I of
the Byzantine Empire.
Let's have a clean election.
See you next time.