[AKANE] In one month, the long
awaited royal election
will finally take place.
Look! It's Kanade!
Oh, good morning, Princess!
[STUDENT 11C]
Have a wonderful day, Princess!
Thanks, you, too.
I bet you're excited
about next month.
You've got my vote, Kanade.
I know you'll win for sure!
That means a lot.
But, there's still
plenty of time left.
Please be sure to consider
your choice carefully.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[STUDENT 11D] Is it just
me or is there something
different about her?
Have you noticed anything?
[STUDENT 11E] Yeah, she's
nicer than she was before.
More mellow.
I used to be so
afraid to talk to her
even when she was smiling.
It's good to see that she's
let her guard down a little.
[AKANE, KAREN]
Uh?
I can't thank you enough.
I feel like a jerk asking
a princess to help, though.
[MISAKI]
Please don't.
With the extra hands,
it'll be done in a flash.
No problem at all.
[OLD MAN 11A]
It's certainly appreciated.
Beru, get back to work!
[gasps]
[MISAKI]
Clean now, nap later, got it?
[BERU groans]
[KAREN]
Man, she's really working hard.
I've seen Misaki and her
clones helping people
all over the place lately.
For real.
[SATO]
Akane!
[KAREN, AKANE]
Huh?
[AKANE]
Hey, Hana! Is Shu campaigning?
That's right.
We're going to the
north side park next.
No rest for the royal and weary.
You need to keep up your energy.
We still have three more
places to visit today.
[SHU] Are you kidding me?
Man, that's rough!
[BOTH giggle]
Well, we're off.
Catch you later!
Everyone's working
so hard lately.
That's true.
Huh?
And you're working just as hard.
[KAREN]
Hey. Do you remember that day?
[AKANE]
Hm?
[TERU sighs] I think Jackal will
behave after that feast.
After six helpings,
you should be
the one doing the dishes,
not poor Akane.
[TERU]
I couldn't help it!
You should've heard him roaring
during my speech today!
[SHIORI]
That was your stomach, Teru.
[HIKARI]
One month left.
Everyone's got a
head start on me.
I need to step up
my game, big time.
Haruka! I really
need your advice!
[AKANE]
I don't believe it.
Even Hikari is starting
to take things seriously!
Could you be more specific?
So...
Top Idol is next month
and I wanna win it!
Do you have any
strategies I could use?
[AKANE]
She's in her own little world.
[NEWSCASTER 1B]
As always,
we'll close with the
public opinion poll.
[NEWSCASTER 1A]
The immovable Aoi is still
in first, but Princess
Akane is closing in.
[sighs] Man, Aoi,
you're amazing.
You've been in first since
the start of this thing
and you haven't had
to do a single speech
or campaign rally.
The people really like you.
[giggles]
Akane's 100th speech was today.
Here's a glimpse for those
of you that missed it.
Shank you. Thish meats sho mush.
[BOY FAN CLUB]
Akane forever!
[KANADE] A hundred times,
and you still can't
get through the first sentence.
[NEWSCASTER 1A]
Princess Kanade made a return
to the third spot after a
recent surge of new supporters.
But catching up with
Aoi will be difficult.
Princess Misaki is in fourth.
[groans] After all of that,
she still got ahead of me?
[NEWSCASTER 1A] Shiori in
seventh, Haruka in eighth,
and Teru in nineth.
Prince Shu saw a notable
increase in support last month,
but it's not enough to
put him in the top three.
[sighs]
Our ranks may have switched,
but the numbers are
still pretty close.
[MISAKI] Somehow that doesn't
make me feel better.
[HARUKA]
Well, you haven't been doing
as many speeches, remember?
Why not?
She's had some trouble making
it to the speech sites.
She keeps stopping to
help out the citizens.
Yeah, I saw her cleaning up
the park this afternoon.
[HARUKA] She helped some new
neighbors move yesterday.
The day before that,
she unloaded cargo
at the fish market.
And, last week,
she even volunteered
to hand out tissues and flyers
at a local convenience store.
So, I like helping people.
It's not a big deal.
Well. I happen to think it's
one of your best qualities.
[gasps]
Keep doing what
you think is best,
and you'll be just fine.
[gasps]
If Haruka says so, then it
must be true. Be proud.
'Kay.
Just "Keep doing what
you think is best," huh?
[SHU]
I'm home.
[AOI] Welcome home.
Do you need dinner?
Nah. I'm good.
Why were you late?
I walked Hana home first.
It must be nice,
having a girl like her
organizing your schedule.
Talk about a sweetheart.
You've sure got it easy.
And on top of that, my numbers
have gone up, as well.
[KANADE]
It's good to be you.
[growls] I don't get it!
Every single one of
my brothers and sisters
were able to increase their
numbers over the past month.
But mine haven't changed!
I busted my butt and only
went up one lousy point!
That's still one point, Teru!
Yep! Nothing to scoff at.
You should be proud, bro.
[TERU] I see the pity
behind your smiles,
and I don't like it!
Go ahead! Tell me I've lost!
Darn it.
How am I supposed to protect
what's precious to me
if I can't overcome this?
Do I still not have the
strength to become king?
[TERU gasps]
Big brother, you'll always
be the best to me.
Huh?
At being too stubborn.
[TERU] Wow. And here I thought
I couldn't feel any worse.
Life is so cruel.
Hey, gathering lots of
supporters is one thing.
But it's important
to remember that
even a single vote is special.
You think so?
[HARUKA]
People will notice when you show
gratitude for their support.
And that will lead
to more support later.
Five or ten years down
the road, that one vote
could transform into
over 10,000 votes.
[SHIORI]
Wow, that many? That's amazing!
So cool!
I bet you got that number
by using your special power,
am I right?
Not at all.
[AKANE]
'Kay, me next!
What can I do to
improve my chances?
Stop fumbling your speeches
before you start them.
I knew you'd say that.
You've had a problem with
being in the spotlight
for a long time, Akane.
Try cutting yourself
some slack, okay?
[AKANE]
But I have to get over this now!
If I don't become king, I'll
never get rid of the cameras,
and I'll never
live a quiet life!
She thinks becoming
king will get her
out of the public eye?
Something tells me
she hasn't really
thought this through at all.
Hey. I've always wondered this.
Why is it you hate being
in the limelight so much?
[gasps]
It's because... I...
Wait just a minute.
You weren't like this
when we were little.
You were totally fine with
being in front of people.
Man, I wonder what happened.
Huh?
[HIKARI]
Come on! Tell us.
By the way, there's
a new park open--
I can tell you guys why.
Don't you dare!
[SHU]
Hey.
Kanade...
[KANADE]
I've had a rough past, too.
But I was able to let that go.
[KANADE] At the time,
Akane was a little older
than Teru is now.
The surveillance cameras
hadn't been installed,
back then. We didn't
think there was a need.
Where evil strikes,
I'll be there to stop it!
[SHU]
You're such a dork.
You do know you're not
really a superhero, right?
Yeah, whatever!
If I use my powers,
all bad guys can do
is poop their pants!
[SHU] Mom says you're being
reckless with your ability.
If you don't control yourself,
you'll get into trouble.
But I have control!
[sighs]
I'll be back.
Going on patrol?
No, to Karen's house!
Her mom's at work, so
I'm keeping her company
while she's home alone.
Don't follow me, okay?
[KUSUNOKI]
I'm afraid we have to, Princess.
The king has asked
that the guards
escort you if you wish
to leave the castle.
He was quite insistent.
I'm sorry, but those
are the rules.
I'll be totally fine.
I'm just going to play
at a friend's house.
But, you're still
leaving the castle.
Your father is only
trying to protect you.
He's worried about you.
Especially after
the way you've been
using your powers in public.
He would hate for you
to hurt yourself.
Okay, fine! I get it!
[AKANE grumbles] If I show up
at Karen's with a bunch
of scary guards around me,
she'll be too afraid to play!
[KAREN sobbing]
[gasps]
[KANADE] In the end,
Akane found a way give
the suits the slip, and
went to Karen's by herself.
[GUARD 11A]
I can't go any farther.
When will your mom
be home from work?
I'm not sure.
She said it would be
pretty late. It's fine.
I won't be afraid now
that you're here, Akane.
[giggles] Monsters and bad
guys are no match for me!
[KAREN, AKANE giggle]
--So, what should we play first?
--[rattling]
What's that?
[AKANE]
I thought no one was home.
[KAREN]
There's not supposed to be.
Dad? That yo--
[whimeprs]
Who is that?
It's a stranger!
I think he's, uh--
--He's a...
--[THIEF 11A] Crap.
...a burgler!
[whimpers]
[THIEF 11A] Keep quiet
and you won't get hurt.
All right, little ladies?
Hey!
[groans]
[BOTH panting]
Huh?!
Oh, no, there's another one!
In here!
Those little brats!
Okay, big guy, go get 'em!
Huh?
What do we do?
Don't you worry!
I'm gonna make these
creeps sorry they ever
set foot in your house!
S'that so? I'd like
to see ya try.
[grunting]
[laughs] We still
ain't sorry, squirt.
[THIEF 11A]
Missed me!
[AKANE]
Get out!
[THIEF 11A] What are you
aimin' at? The wall?
[THIEVES yelp]
[yells]
[THIEVES whimper]
[THIEVES yell]
[THIEF 11A]
That's new.
We don't got time
to be gawkin' here!
Let's get 'em!
[yells]
[AKANE]
Take that! Hi-ya! Kapow!
I'm the protector of
peace in this country!
Give up, losers!
[growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[THIEF 11A] I was gonna go easy
on ya 'cause you're kids,
but no more Mr. Nice Guy!
[KAREN, AKANE whimper]
[whimpering]
[THIEF 11A grunts]
[AKANE screams]
[THIEVES groan]
--[GUARD 11A] That's Akane!
--[GUARD 11B] Princess!
--[THIEVES groaning]
--[AKANE screaming]
[THIEVES]
All right, we're guilty!
Just get us away
from that monster!
--[KAREN sobbing]
--[GUARD 11A] Yes, that's right.
Princess Akane and
her friend are safe.
Requesting immediate pick-up.
[KAREN]
I was so scared!
[inhales]
[MAN 11A]
Isn't that Princess Akane?
[WOMAN 11A]
You're right! Why is she here?
[WOMAN 11B]
Wait, you don't think
she wrecked the place, do you?
[GIRL 11A]
No way.
She was rescuing her friend.
[MAN 11B] Doesn't look
like a rescue to me.
[MAN 11C] How could a
little kid pull that off?
[MAN 11D] Show some
respect! She's royalty!
[MAN 11E]
That doesn't excuse...
[AKANE]
Stop staring at me!
[AOI] From that day on, Akane
did everything she could
to avoid drawing
attention to herself.
[MISAKI]
I get it.
So that's the reason Dad
had surveillance cameras
put up all over the city.
[SHU]
Yeah, it is.
Hold on.
You stopped the burglars,
so what was the problem?
[AKANE]
I hated it.
[HIKARI] Why? Everyone
thought you were cool!
I didn't feel that way.
It's too scary being
in the spotlight.
[HIKARI]
You think so?
[AKANE]
Yeah. At least, for me it is.
But becoming king won't
solve the problem.
If anything, it'll make
things even worse for you.
[phone rings]
[AOI gasps]
Hello?
What? Dad's hurt?
[ALL gasp]
[AKANE]
You strained your back?
[SOICHIRO]
Heh...
[KANADE]
What did you do?
[SATSUKI] Your father got
a little over-zealous
trying to carry me
around the castle.
[KUSUNOKI]
My deepest apologies.
I'm afraid your father was too
fast for us to stop him in time.
[sighs] At least it's not major.
I panicked when they
told me you couldn't move.
It wasn't an exaggeration.
The lug was in so much pain,
he got stuck in mid-lift.
[sighs] I'm in shock.
I can't believe I married
such a colossal goofball!
Are you going to be okay, Daddy?
Yes, dear, don't you worry.
[HARUKA] He'll be stuck
in bed for a while, though.
There's no time. I have to--
[groans]
Please, Your Highness.
You'll make it worse!
I still have my duties!
But if you keep forcing it,
you'll end up stuck
in bed even longer.
[groans]
Listen to us.
If you want to heal, then
you need to get your rest.
[SOICHIRO] If I do that, it will
affect the citizens' livelihood.
I can't afford to let
my body get the best of me.
Uh, Kusunoki?
Are things really as bad as
he's making them out to be?
Yes. Perhaps even more so.
We've planned a
banquet to welcome
some foreign dignitaries'
tomorrow night.
And we still have to
finalize the paperwork
for next year's budget.
Not to mention the interviews.
On top of that,
he was supposed to pay
a sympathy visit
to a small town.
Why? What happened?
[KUSUNOKI]
Disaster.
The residents are
completely cut off from aid.
A landslide blocked the only
road that could reach them.
Gee, Daddy, you really do
have the worst timing.
That's why I can't
be idling about!
[screams]
[AKANE]
We said don't move!
There's still hope. We're
all Sakuradas, aren't we?
Don't you think we're
capable of handling things
in Dad's place for a day or two?
[gasps]
[MISAKI] Yeah! Why didn't
I think of that?
[AOI] In that case, I'll
entertain the dignitaries
and host the banquet.
[KANADE] Then, I'll take
care of the annual budget.
[HARUKA]
I'll help you with that.
[MISAKI] You can leave
the interviews to me!
[HIKARI] You guys can deal
with the boring stuff.
I'll babysit Shiori
and hold down the fort!
[SHIORI]
I'll make dinner for everyone!
I'll go visit the village.
Take me! Jackal and
I can help you!
Come on, I don't wanna just
sit here and do nothing.
[SHU]
Cool. Let's go.
[gasps] 'Kay!
What should I do? Stay here?
You can help us with
the relief efforts.
No!
There's no way I could cheer up
a town full of strangers.
[SHU] All right then,
can you entertain
a score of foreign politicians?
[AKANE]
Not a chance!
[SHU] Then, how about
a massive press interview
in a room filled with cameras?
[AKANE]
I would die!
[SHU]
Then, that settles it.
Cheer up. The people
really like you.
Everyone in that village
could use your strength.
You think I'm strong? Seriously?
[SHU]
What a mess.
This is way too much
for three guys to handle.
Let me. I'll have this
cleared in no time, bro.
It's too dangerous!
Chill, I got this. I can
cut loose for a change.
Let me show everyone what
I'm really capable of.
Teru...
Just don't do
anything rash, cool?
Roger.
[TERU yelling]
All right then, let's go.
Right.
[VILLAGE MAYOR 11A]
This is quite an honor!
You're most welcome, Prince Shu.
Thank you. You too,
Princess Aka--
I'm the red flower of justice!
Ah! You must be
Scarlet Bloom.
Everyone. We're
honored to be here.
Especially at such
a desperate time.
Our father had planned to
visit you all himself,
but a sudden illness
prevented that.
It's all right.
We're just happy that someone
from the royal family showed up!
It means more to us
than you could ever know.
We were afraid we
had been forgotten,
but here you are,
watching over us all.
It's enough to melt my heart!
Do you have any provision
or medical needs?
[VILLAGE MAYOR 11A]
We're a tough lot, sire.
Just knowing that you care
will help us through.
I'd like some water.
[MOTHER 11A]
Quiet! You're being rude!
--[VILLAGERS gasp]
--Where did he go?
[VILLAGERS gasp]
Drink up.
I think I'm going senile.
I hope it's not too much.
[VILLAGERS laugh]
[SHU]
Hm?
[laughing coninues]
[VILLAGE MAYOR 11A]
Thanks for that.
It's been a while since
we've had a good laugh.
I'm glad I could help.
[VILLAGE MAYOR 11A] Ever since
the road was blocked off,
we've been on edge. We didn't
know how we'd survive.
But it shouldn't be long
until the road is
free to use again.
[TERU]
We're here!
Hey. That was pretty quick.
See, I told you
I could handle it.
The road's good as new now.
Man, I've never seen
anything like it before.
You can hardly tell
there was a landslide!
Thank you for everything, sire.
How can we ever repay you?
Oh, you don't have to do that.
I'm just glad I could help.
[SHU chuckles]
[AKANE]
Shu and Teru are amazing.
It's my turn. All right!
There we go!
[YOUNG GIRLS]
Thanks, Scarlet Bloom!
[AKANE grunting]
--[CAT 11A meowing]
--[CHILDREN gasping]
Whew.
[CHILDREN chattering]
Aw, it was nothin'.
Princess Akane!
You dropped these.
Dropped wha--? Akane?
I didn't realize they
had fallen off my face!
Wait. How long?
The whole time.
[AKANE shieks]
No way!
[YOUNG GIRL 11E]
Uh-huh! Yes, way!
[AKANE]
I don't understand.
Was I really that focused
on helping everyone?
[AKANE gasps]
Thanks for everything, Princess.
You're welcome.
[giggles]
[gasps]
[AKANE]
I think... I get it.
[KAREN]
Hey. Do you remember that day?
When you stopped the thieves.
You never let go of me,
so I knew I was safe.
[AKANE]
Oh. I guess I did.
[KAREN] To this day,
I can still remember
what your hand
felt like in mine.
Your strength and warmth
made me feel like
I could face anything that
life had to throw at me.
As long as you were by my side.
[AKANE] That's it, I don't need
a secret identity anymore.
I can let it go.
[AKANE]
I'll never forget you.
Thanks. And goodbye,
Scarlet Bloom.
Hey, don't litter.
[AKANE]
Sorry.
[KUSUNOKI]
That is all.
[SOICHIRO]
Hm. Good.
[SOICHIRO] They've grown
into reliable adults.
[SATSUKI] Hmph. I wonder
where they get that from.
[NEWSCASTER 1B]
Here are the results
for today's opinion poll.
Prince Shu and Princess Akane
have increased their supporters,
putting Princesses Aoi,
Akane, Kanade and Prince Shu
in a four-way battle!
Who will take the crown?
You see?
That point turned into
12 in just one week.
Yeah!
The rest of you better
keep your guard up!
You must have made a
good impression, Teru.
[giggles] Ah! Hey, Haruka?
There's something that I've
been wanting to ask you about.
You already know which one
of us will be king, don't you?
[gasps]
[HARUKA]
I know the odds.
But there are always surprises.
[AKANE]
I'm the third daughter, Akane!
[SATSUKI] Akane may be easily
embarrassed sometimes,
but her shy nature makes her
very empathetic towards others.
She's also quite dependable.
[AKANE]
I don't know about that.
[SATSUKI] If she became
king, our country would
be a place of
peace and kindness.
So, what's your campaign
promise, sweetie?
[AKANE]
To destroy all cameras!
I want to make a nation
where people feel safe
without having to be watched!
By the way, the king that
I look up to the most
is Henry IV of France.
I hope I have your
vote next month!