[NEWSCASTER 1B] You're watching
Sakurada Family News.
The country's only source
for all things royalty.
[NEWSCASTER 1A]
After months of anticipation,
the election for the nation's
next king is this weekend.
Before the ballots open,
we'll hear one last speech
from each of the
nine candidates.
[NEWSCASTER 1B] Those that
are interested in voting
will finally get
the chance to support
their favorite
prince or princess.
And remember,
your vote has the
power to change...
[NEWSCASTERS]
...our future!
[FUKUSHINA] At last.
The elections have arrived.
I can truly give support
to my dearest Akane.
If all goes well,
and she becomes king...
Oh, hi. I'm King Akane.
Thanks for having me.
She'll be the cutest ruler ever!
Um. Plastic, please.
The sovereign of shyness!
[AKANE yelps]
[FUKUSHINA] Sorry, this
fantasy is for my eyes only.
[AKANE]
Morning, Fukushina!
[FUKUSHINA]
Good Morning. Sakurada.
You look distracted.
[FUKUSHINA] Oh, I was just
admiring the spring weather.
Are you walking to school
by yourself today?
That's right.
I had to learn to get
over my shyness sometime,
or I'd be pretty
useless as a king.
[gasps]
[FUKUSHINA]
The Sakurada that I once loved--
the ever-nervous idol of
our fan club has changed!
No, she's finally
made a breakthrough!
I need to support her,
like a good friend should!
Well, I'll see you later!
[FUKUSHINA] She may not be the
same, but she's still... great!
[KAREN]
Okay.
Everyone's gonna get
out and vote, right?
[STUDENT 12A]
Yeah! You know it!
[STUDENT 12B] I didn't wait
this long for nothin'.
Then, please vote for Akane!
And thanks a lot!
[STUDENT 12C]
Well, duh.
[STUDENT 12D]
After all, we're her classmates.
[STUDENT 12E] Like we're
not gonna vote for her?
[STUDENT 12F]
I planned to from the start.
Thanks so much, guys!
I'll do my best!
Karen... An...
You'll cheer for me during
my speech, won't you?
Of course we will, goofball.
Did you decide what
you're going to say?
Uh. I've almost
got it figured out.
You liar!
[AKANE]
What to say.
No pressure, it's just the
culmination of all my speeches,
so it has to be good.
I wonder if the others are
having this much trouble?
I'm sorry to hold you up.
Especially during
your lunch break.
Please.
It's my honor to help you
as much as I can, President.
Uh, I mean, Uzuki.
Graduation will be here
before we know it,
so I wanted to get things
organized before then.
Makes sense.
[UZUKI]
I'm leaving everything to you,
Miss Student Council President.
Right.
I'll follow your example
and do my best.
Good. You better!
[BOTH giggle]
[UZUKI]
Thanks for your help.
I can take the rest from here.
You should get back to
preparing for the election.
[KANADE] No worries. I finished
my prep work ages ago.
Including the script
for my final speech.
'Course you did. If you
don't mind me asking,
what are you gonna talk about?
[KANADE]
Well.
How I'd build my kingdom,
by my authority,
and exactly the way
I want it to be.
A dictatorship?
I thought about it,
but I changed my mind.
You still thought about it.
[KANADE] After watching
my siblings work hard
and grow over the past year,
I've realized that
everything's different.
Including me.
That's why I changed my mind.
[KANADE]
They're so strong.
I want everyone in the world
to see my brothers and sisters
through my eyes.
Aoi, who keeps to herself
and watches over all of us.
Shu, who takes charge
when he needs to,
and always thinks of
everyone's welfare.
Akane, who, despite her shyness,
cares deeply for others.
Misaki, who can't stand idly by
when there's someone in need.
Haruka supports
us and never asks
for anything in return.
Hikari is doing her own thing.
But she's working hard at it.
Teru: Young and brave,
with boundless determination.
And, Shiori,
whose kind heart has
room for everyone.
[KANADE] When people vote,
I want them to do so
because they truly know us.
Kanade...
I know it will be a
wonderful speech, for sure.
[KANADE gasps]
Enough about that.
Let's finish cleaning
up, President.
You're the president
now, remember, silly?
Wait. Kanade really said that?
[UZUKI]
Yup!
[NANAO]
Aw, Man.
If that's some new strategy,
it's working because now
I wanna vote for her.
Yeah, no joke.
It's hard to pick one candidate
when they'd all
make great kings.
[UZUKI]
Right?
Sorry it's so difficult.
If it's any consolation,
you can blame my father.
[laughing]
[AOI]
Just think it over
and vote for whomever
you feel is best.
If you say so.
[NANAO]
What if you win?
[AOI gasps]
[UZUKI]
Nanao?
Do you really wanna
dance to the tempo
that your father set for
the rest of your life?
I don't know.
[NANAO]
Forget I said it.
[SHIZURU]
Aoi? No matter what happens,
I'll be with you all the way.
Yeah! Me, too!
[NANAO] Tough break. I'm afraid
you're stuck with us now.
You better get used to having
a dose of crazy around,
"Your Highness."
[SATO]
All right!
[HITOMI] You're stressing
out way too much.
[SAOTOME]
It's true.
[SATO]
But it's almost election day!
I need to bring my A-game!
[sighs] Well.
I guess that I could get used to
seeing Shu sitting
on the throne.
[SAOTOME]
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
Your support means
the world to both of us!
[SHU]
Thank you, you, you, you.
Then again, if he
does become king,
his schedule will be more
crowded than ever before.
[SATO]
Maybe.
Which means he'll probably have
even less time to
spend with you, right?
[SATO yelps]
Hey.
No need to worry,
with the two of us around,
you won't even miss him.
[SAOTOME]
Mm-hm!
New plan.
I have to stop Shu from
becoming king at all costs!
Chill. We were just joking.
[SATO]
The nerve of those two.
That's not something
to joke about.
Don't you think so, too?
Uh, hey. You in there?
I wouldn't like it.
Not being able to spend
time with the people
I care about, I mean.
It's gonna be fine.
However the election ends,
I have no intention
of letting you feel
lonely for a second.
[SATO gasps]
[SATO]
You're the best, Shu.
Know what?
I think I'm the happiest person
on the planet right now.
[SHU]
Think so?
I could have sworn
I was the happiest.
[SATO]
Well, maybe we're even.
So, what is this for?
Silly.
It's our little way of thanking
you for helping us out so much.
And when the ballots open,
we'll all be voting for you.
[MISAKI gasps]
Thank you so much.
We're gonna be cheering for you
with everything we've got.
Do your best, okay?
Sure!
[BASEBALL PLAYER 5A]
I hope you get the crown!
You'd do wonders
for this country.
I can totally see you helping
everyone the same way
you helped us.
You really think so?
Thanks for your support.
We can't possibly lose, now.
No fair, Misaki.
I wish I had a
charming older brother
like Haruka.
[HARUKA] I'm her younger
brother, actually.
[SPORTS CLUB GIRLS murmuring]
[HARUKA] I know something's
up. You got quiet.
[MISAKI] It's just-- I can't
help but think that this
was a wasted effort
on their part.
Huh? What for?
[MISAKI] Aoi and the others.
Kana, Akane, and Shu.
They have the best shot
at winning this thing.
But I guess you
already knew that.
[MISAKI chuckles]
It's okay.
I'm used to not living up
to people's expectations.
[HARUKA]
You're wrong.
My power just allows me
to see possibilities.
They're far from definite.
Besides,
if you don't become the
next king, that's okay.
You'll still be the same
person you've always been.
Someone I respect and love.
[gasps] I'll do it, Haruka!
I'll win this thing
even if it kills me!
Though, sometimes
you're just weird.
[sighs]
You keep doing that.
Is there something you'd
like to talk about?
[HIKARI]
No, it's nothing.
[MATSUOKA]
Hm.
[SACCHY] She says that
but I know I'd be nervous
if I were in her shoes.
This could change her future.
Not to mention our
nation's future.
[sighs]
[MATSUOKA]
If I may, Princess.
Perhaps it would be best
for you to take a break
from performing until after
the election is over.
No way! I won't do it!
Why not?
[HIKARI]
Because!
I wouldn't get first place
in the general idol election!
[MATSUOKA, SACCHY] Wha--? That's
what you were worried about?!
[SATSUKI]
"That is my solemn promise
as a member of
the royal family."
Well, Mom, how is it?
[SATSUKI] Good! This is
wonderfully written.
You really think so?
I'm so proud of you, Teru!
Yes. I can tell you
worked hard on it.
Shiori, did you help your
brother write this speech?
[SHIORI]
Mm-hm!
'Scuse me.
We could use your
help, Ms. Dictionary.
[DICTIONARY 12A]
Of course! What do you need?
Just a little.
[TERU]
Hey, Mom?
[SATSUKI]
Hm?
[TERU]
I'm glad you like it, but--
Do you think I should write more
about my campaign promises?
[AKANE, MISAKI, AOI,
KANADE gasp]
Teru?
[SATSUKI]
It's fine as is.
Don't push yourself so much.
You're still in
elementary school.
But the people should
know that I wanna
become king to
protect everyone, and--
I think that the citizens
want to hear your true feelings.
So instead of making promises,
you should speak from
your heart. That way,
no matter what happens,
you'll know you were honest.
Not only with the people,
but with yourself.
[TERU]
You really think so, Mom?
[SATSUKI]
Yes. Now, it's time for dinner.
Everyone help set up the table.
[KIDS]
Okay!
[SOICHIRO]
You're sure about this?
Yes.
Very well. I understand,
believe me.
I'm sorry.
There's no need to be. Now then.
I'll make the announcement
public before the ceremonies--
No. Please let me do it.
I want to be the
one to tell them.
[SOICHIRO]
All right.
I'm going to bed.
I'm proud of you, Aoi.
Absolute Obedience is
a most seductive power.
It takes a special kind of
person not to abuse it.
But you've handled it very well.
[AOI]
Thanks, Dad. Goodnight.
Are you really okay
with this, dear?
If it's what Aoi wants,
then absolutely.
I was an only child.
My path was decided
before I was born.
But our children have choices.
[SATSUKI]
Was that your plan?
[SOICHIRO]
Who knows?
[MR. MASHIMA] The hour
is upon us, and thousands
of eager voters have
flocked to Sakurada castle.
Soon, we'll hear the
candidate's final speeches
and watch as history unfolds.
Now then.
Let's go into the crowd and get
some thoughts from the public.
Would you mind telling us
who you're voting for?
For Hikari! Oh, sorry.
I mean, the fifth princess.
We all go to the
same school together.
That's so sweet.
Well, I hope she gets elected!
[GIRLS]
Me, too!
Excuse me, would you care
to comment on the cadidates--
[FUKUSHINA]
Let's get pumped!
[BOY FAN CLUB]
Go!
[MR. MASHIMA]
On second thought, never mind.
That's all from Sakurada castle.
Such enthusiasm!
Yes. Now, onto the--
Wow, things are getting
crazy out there.
You were expecting
them to be calm?
Oh, this is nothing
compared to my concerts.
[TERU]
You're so brave, sis!
[HIKARI chuckles]
[TERU]
My tummy feels weird.
Like there's some
kind of monster
about to burst out of my chest!
Drown it. Quickly.
You're just nervous.
It's totally natural.
[TERU]
Are you sure that's it?
[AOI]
There. All done!
Thanks you. It looks perfect!
Well, what do you think?
Do I pull off this hairdo?
It's the same style
you always have.
C'mon, there's no
need to be bashful.
[AOI giggles]
Would you knock it off?
Yes?
[KUSUNOKI]
Pardon me. Well.
It's time for your
final speeches.
[ALL gasp]
[SHU]
It's the moment of truth.
But before we go, let's decide
who's going out first.
We could always draw lots.
You know that I won't win!
I think we should go by age!
[HIKARI]
That means you, Shiori!
[HARUKA] We can't start
from the youngest!
[TERU]
You okay with that?
[SHIORI]
Yup.
[AOI]
Hold it. I'll go.
What I have to say
can't wait anymore.
I've already told Father
and he gave me his blessing.
[AOI]
People of the nation.
Thank you for coming. I am Aoi,
eldest daughter
and first princess
of the Sakurada royal family.
First, I would like to
apologize for any disturbances
our campaigns may have
caused over the past year.
This may come as
a surprise, but,
after a great deal of
thought, I've decided...
...to remove myself
from candidacy.
--[TERU gasps]
--No way!
I have many reasons.
But key among them was the
discovery of my true power.
[gasps]
[AOI] This ability,
"Absolute Obedience,"
forces people to
obey my every word.
[gasps]
If I were elected the king,
I would be forced
to give many orders
to various people
during my reign.
[AOI] However, I do not
trust that those orders
would always be appropriate.
So the throne should
be out of my reach.
Also, after living
among you for so long,
I realized something
very important.
I want a normal life,
with the people I love.
--You go, Aoi.
--[AOI] From now on,
I will continue to
serve our nation.
But I will do so as
a normal citizen,
and create my own path in life.
[gasps]
[AOI]
What the--
[MAN 12A]
It's flying too low!
[MAN 12B] It's gonna
crash into the castle!
What is happening?
Respond at once!
[PILOT 12A]
I'm sorry! I can't hold it.
[KUSUNOKI] Your Majesties,
please take cover.
Our security will
handle the crowds.
[SHU]
I'll be right back.
[AKANE, HIKARI, AOI gasp]
[PILOT 12A groans]
Hey, are you all right?
[GIRL 12A]
Momma!
[SHU] He's not well. Let's
get the medics up here.
[KUSUNOKI]
Sire!
[SHU]
Shiori, can you help me?
[SHIORI]
Mm-hm.
We'll take care of this, Dad.
Go.
I'll help, too!
[AOI]
Be careful, Akane!
I will!
Thank you, Miss.
She says you need to
push the red button
and then pull the
lever toward you.
Good work.
This doesn't seem all that hard.
[SHIORI gasps]
[sighs, gasps] We're gonna hit!
--[SHIORI yelps]
--[SHU grunts]
[HARUKA]
You okay up there?
Kinda.
What's wrong, Miss Airship?
[AIRSHIP 12A]
I'm wounded.
I'm afraid I won't be able
to fly for long. I'm sorry.
[SHIORI] She says she
can't fly much longer.
I need to land this
thing. Got any ideas?
It's absolute chaos down here.
Landing isn't an option.
[KANADE]
Aoi, wait.
[AOI]
Why?
You'll go back on your word
if you use your power.
We got this.
Just leave it all to us, sis!
I don't mind working
hard when I need to.
[SHU chuckles] First, find a
spot I can set this down
within five minutes.
You got it.
[SHU] Second, can you
broadcast my transmission
to the crowd?
Huh?
[AKANE]
Okay.
Trying to control something
this big was a bad idea.
[SHU]
Your attention, please.
This is Prince Shu
of the royal family.
Please, remain calm
and listen to me.
As I speak, my siblings and I
--are working to protect you.
--[SATO] Be careful. Shu.
[SHU]
We won't fail.
There's someone among
you that I love.
I want to give her a life filled
with laughter and smiles.
Think of your loved ones.
Of someone that you
want to protect.
The way you feel for them is
the same way we feel for you.
Please, let us do
what we were born to.
Trust in our powers, and allow
us to serve you the way
a royal family should, so that
everyone can live a life
filled with laughter and smiles.
All right, let's get to work!
Time to shine!
[HIKARI]
Ta-dah! Laito is on the case!
Everyone! Please move
in an orderly fashion!
[HIKARI]
This way, boys!
[IDOL FANBOYS]
Laito!
[HARUKA] How about the
lake near the castle?
No go. There are too many boats.
Akane can't hold it forever.
Come on! Think! Time is limited.
[KANADE]
Will this work?
[HARUKA]
Hope so.
To be honest, this barely
qualifies as a plan.
[KANADE] Half a chance is
better than none, right?
It's here!
[TERU gasps]
[KANADE]
They're coming in way too fast!
[SHU]
There it is.
You two doing okay?
Might get bumpy.
Yeah. Good to go.
I need a nap.
[SHU]
Brace yourselves. Here we go!
[grunts]
[yelling] Stop!
[TERU sighs]
[panting]
[SHU gasps]
[laughs] Who wants to go again?
[BOTH giggle]
[CROWD cheers]
[AKANE] What a relief.
I wasn't sure we'd make it.
[SHU] Really? I never
doubted it for a second.
[AKANE] You know, Shu,
sometimes I wonder
if you're courageous
or just thick headed.
[SHU]
Ouch. That was harsh.
[AKANE] But I gotta admit,
your speech was cool.
[SHU]
Thanks.
[AKANE]
Can I ask you something?
[SHU]
What's up?
[AKANE] Why didn't you use your
power to teleport the blimp?
[SHU]
Oh.
[AKANE]
Yup. Thick headed.
[KUSUNOKI] The one who bears
this crown protects truth,
justice, and peace
throughout the land.
And embodies faith,
idealism, and nobility.
Do you swear to lead
this nation through
harmony and through
discord, and bring hope
to its people for as
long as you shall reign?
I swear.
[KUSUNOKI]
Shu Sakurada.
I appoint you the
successor to the throne.
Shu.
Yeah? What's up?
[SOICHIRO]
Do your best.
[SHU]
I will!
[AKANE] And so, after lots
of learning and growing,
our year of campaigning
came to an end.
Aoi moved out for
college and is enjoying
living a normal life
with her friends.
Shu finally introduced
his girlfriend, Hana,
to Mom and Dad.
Kana hit the books hard,
and is planning to go
to medical school.
Misaki became her
middle school's
student council president.
She elected Haruka as
secretary to keep him nearby.
After the election,
Hikari revealed
that she was Laito.
Luckily, it didn't
hurt her idol career
and she's still going strong.
Teru and Shiori decided
they wanted to help Shu
at the castle,
so they're studying under
Kusonoki's tutelage.
As for me--
Okay, I'm heading out!
Be careful.
Have a great day!
[AKANE] I haven't changed as
drastically as the others.
[AKANE]
Huh?
When did you get here, fella?
[AKANE] But I still feel
like I've blossomed.
If even just a little.