Wow!
Amazing!
It's still going!
Wow, it took off in no time at all!
Yeah, and look at how high it can go!
Huh?
Hey! Here let me see it!
Wow!
Come on! Let me have it!
Hahaha!
It can fly at 10,000 meters for 30 minutes!
How about that?
Well I'm sure it's a world record for a drone but...
Running something at that altitude...
How would it even be possible to operate?
He's using satellite communication.
That's the way he's controlling it even from so far away.
Hmm.
In order to fly, the unit
relies on the images it receives.
As well as it's latitude and longitude coordinates.
But you've got to operate the direction,
speed, and camera, all at the same time.
So it takes some getting used to.
But what's the purpose of building a drone like that?
Are you kidding me?
That sort of thing is ever man's dream come true!
With this, you can climb to the top of Mt. Everest
without ever having to take a single step, right?
Oho! Ho ho ho ho!
Wow, that laugh isn't creepy at all.
Or, it's an invention that could
become a giant legal headache.
When we return from this commercial break,
We've got the latest news on the upcoming Tokyo Summit.
I'm outside of the international conference hall
where the summit will be taking place next week!
A resort built on a landfill on Tokyo
Bay, the Edge of Ocean, will open next month.
A vast compound of diverse facilities,
it was designed to mimic a coastal community!
Incorporating the use of water as a central focal point!
The Casino is designed in a seashell motif,
and also serves as a light house to keep watch over ships.
A full view of the Edge of Ocean can be enjoyed from here!
And over at the shopping mall near the Casino Tower,
there is a large waterfall and a peaceful garden
that welcomes residents, employees, and visitors.
Quite a sight to behold!
The other concept is Harmony.
Inside, the conference hall employs the
understated splendor and beauty, of a Japanese Garden.
And on the first floor,
there are several adjoining trendy
and stylish restaurants to choose from.
Two convenient monorails make rounds on the premises.
One on the upper level, and the other suspended below.
As you can see, this city smartly
combines the beauty of tradition,
with the technology of the future.
The Edge of Ocean is connected
by two equal length bridges.
The MPD that will be on patrol on the 1st of May,
opening day of the summit,
has announced that they will be dispatching a
whopping 22,000 officers to guard the entire city.
Coming up next, we’ve got the latest
updates on the unmanned probe, "Hakucho"!
I'm Shinichi Kudo, a highschool detective.
I went to an amusement park with my childhood friend Ran.
And while we were there, we witnessed
some men in black making a dangerous deal.
Because I was so absorbed in watching them,
I didn’t notice the man who came at me from behind.
He forced me to drink a poison that
knocked me out, and when I woke up...
...I discovered that my body had shrunk!
If those guys ever found out that Shinichi
Kudo is still alive, they'd come back.
Which would put everyone I know in terrible danger!
So on Doctor Agasa’s advice, I
kept my real identity a secret.
When Ran asked me who I was, I quickly
made up the name, "Conan Edogawa."
I knew if I wanted info on the men in black,
the smart thing would be to stay
at her house with her and her dad,
who ran a detective agency.
Meet Genta, Mitsuhiko, and Ayumi.
After I shrank, they became my friends.
And this is Ai Haibara, her real name is Shiho Miyano.
She used to be a member of the Black Organization,
but she wanted out so she tried to kill herself,
taking the exact same poison I was given,
and it shrank her body too.
Here's another dark figure, also
a part of the Black Organization,
code-named "Bourbon," alias Toru Amuro.
His true identity is chief of the Security Police.
He belongs to the secret institute called “Zero”
part of the National Public Safety Commission.
To camouflage this, he became a student detective
of Kogoro Mori while working at a coffee shop.
He is indeed a man of mystery.
My body may have shrunk, but my I.Q. hasn't.
Detective Conan leaves no case unsolved!
There is always only one truth!
The unmanned probe, Hakucho, once
done collecting samples from Mars,
will finally be making its return
journey to Earth on May 1st, Japan time.
Upon its return home, the probe
itself will burn up during re-entry,
leaving behind only a capsule 4 short meters in diameter,
to safely re-enter the Earth’s atmosphere.
At that point, the capsule will descend by parachute,
and is expected to land in the Pacific Ocean near Japan.
That's fascinating!
Here in the sample capsule,
they’ve put a GPS-controlled device
that’s called the precision guided system.
allowing the capsule to fall
within a radius of 200 meters.
Huh...
Huh?! Wow, woah!
Give it to me!
Come on!
It's my turn!
Let me do it!
You've had it longer!
We gotta take turns!
Woah! Oh!
Hmm...
Maybe I should just divide the remote
control into three parts for them.
Direction, speed, and camera.
Aw man...
We interrupt this broadcast
to bring you some breaking news!
This just in.There’s been a large explosion
at the International Conference Hall...
Where the Tokyo Summit is due to be held next week.
Huh?
This is the image security cameras captured.
What's going on?
Edge of Ocean, a combined
resort compound, is not yet open.
So luckily there were no civilians present at
Hey, Doc!
the facility during the blast.
However, several police officers
who were there in advance to
secure the site for the summit
were either injured or killed.
Again I repeat.
If you're just joining us,
It could be a terrorist attack!
Perhaps... But the summit is next week!
Maybe it was an accident?
... the MPD hasn’t disclosed the number of casualties.
The obvious question remains.
Will this be ruled as a criminal
case or an unfortunate accident?
Some Police have been hurt and
killed... That’s quite serious.
Doc! The display just went black!
Oh, I'll be right there!
Wait a minute... This makes no sense.
If they commit an act of terror prior to
the Summit, then security would get tighter.
Hey, what's wrong?
The security footage... Right after the explosion...
Did you see something weird?
Just for an instant... And I may be wrong about it.
What?
But that man...
He works at Poirot.
I think his name was Toru Amuro.
Wait, that Amuro?!
According to our forensics,
no traces of the explosives were found.
On the first floor of the International
Conference Hall, there is a Japanese restaurant.
The kitchen in its basement is
where the explosion took place.
It was there that they detected a significant gas leak.
It's safe to conclude that this was a gas explosion.
Hold it. That building had recently been completed.
A gas explosion's not possible.
Seemingly. However this gas
pipe is the latest model available.
The tap can even be controlled
and operated through the internet.
Then how the hell could a gas leak even be possible?
It’s may be that the system was already
damaged before it was initially installed.
Weren't there any routine checks?
Actually, there was one scheduled for today.
What do you mean, scheduled today?
The Edge of Ocean’s whole internet
network was going to be set up today.
Yes, after the Public Security and
Safety Bureau did their protocol check,
this was next on their list.
Well if that’s true, then the likelihood
that this was an accident is pretty high.
Mhm, if this were the work of terrorists,
it would be pointless unless executed on May 1st,
the day when heads of state and V.I.P.’s would be there.
And because of today’s incident,
there’s been a venue change.
The Summit will have a new location.
I have a new report.
What is your name and your unit?
I'm Yuya Kazami.
Public Security and Safety Bureau of
MPD. Now, about that gas explosion…
Nothing yet.
They’re checking on the electrical facilities right now.
In regards to the igniter,
it could’ve been a type of high pressure cable.
I see, could it be faulty construction?
No, but...
They found fingerprints burnt on the door of the
storeroom where the high pressure cable was being housed.
Which implies they were there before the explosion?
Yes. The only people who entered
the site were the construction workers,
and our security police team who checked it this morning.
And then we ran all of the
fingerprints through our database.
Prints from constuction workers and police
officers who had been on site were also scanned.
And we found that the prints matched those of someone
formerly employed at the First Investigation Section.
Kogoro Mori.
What?
That's impossible!
Is he joking?
Huh...
That's absurd. How could that be?
The International Conference Hall at the landfill?!
But I've never been there! Not even once!
That may be, but they found your fingerprints at the site.
It can't be! Hmph!
Could it be... that you got drunk again, and
then wandered in there without realizing it?
Absolutely not!
I told you I've never been there!
This is all a mitake! They can look
all they want. They won't find anything!
Please settle down.
This is absurd! I'd never do anything of the kind.
Pardon me.
Oh, okay...
Conan, is something wrong?
That officer there...
His face is injured, is he alright?
Oh, you mean Kazami?
He was one of the officers on
site when the explosion happened.
Hmm...
Huh?
Um, I have to go to the restroom!
Hey, what's up?
Y-Yeah?
Huh? Your dad is being suspected by the police?
Mhm... Though I'm certain this
has to be some kind of a mistake.
Alright then, I'll go check it out on my end.
Using an alternate phone is a real pain.
Wait, where did my phone go?
Hey Doc, are you there?
Hmm?
Oh, hello Shinichi! What's going on?
I'd like to ask you a favor.
Why is this taking them so long?!
Well...
You have to calm down sir.
I want them out of here! Now!!
Huh?
Hm?
My phone...
Man! This is so much fun!
Wait, Genta slow down a little bit! You're going too fast!
We're trying to take picutres here!
Oh, sorry!
But this thing is so awesome!
I mean, can you believe how far it can fly?!
It's got amazing range. As far as 30 kilometers!
Yeah! We flew it from 20 km away just a little while ago!
Did you?
We just delivered something to
my aunt, who lives in Saitama!
Your aunt was really happy, wasn’t she?
Oh... You guys did that?
But, look! That display is so tiny
you can hardly see what’s in it.
Hmm...
It wasn’t really designed to be used by
more than one person at a time, you see.
Hey, Doc, would you be able to
put a display on my controller, too?
I would like to have one too , please!
Hmm...
I suppose I could.
If you can ace this quiz!
Ugh...
Now then. If you answer these correctly
I'll put displays on all of your controllers!
What?!
Ready? Here we go!
In the list of all possible existing hiragana,
which one of these has the largest scale of usage?
Number 1 "A."
Number 2 "Ka."
Number 3 "Sa."
Number 4 "Ta."
But what does that all mean anyway?
It’s simply as I said, the largest scale of usage!
Gosh, that actually sounds kinda complicated…
“A. I. U. E. O.”
“Ka. Ki. Ku. Ke. Ko.”
That should help you figure out the answer.
Sa, Shi, Su, Se, So...
Ta, Chi, Tsu, Te, To.
Huh... I don't know!
Hey, watch it, Ayumi! Quit moving the camera around!
Oh! I'm sorry!
Okay. Here's hint number one.
"Hakucho."
Hakucho?
Oh! You're getting closer?
Hakucho or a Swan...
Brings to mind Swan Lake...
It means big lake, or "Mizuumi"!
Which means the answer is "Mi!"
Wait, what?
Hint number two, "the Hakucho returns."
So are you saying that the Hakucho is going home?
Oh, so it's the lake after all!
A home... A home... House..?
Oooh!!
Yes, I got it!
The unmanned probe, Hakucho, will come back from space!
Right. So the answer is?
The line that starts with "A!"
The hiragana in the middle of this is “U.”
In other words it means “Uchuu,” or “space!”
Cause there’s nothing out there
that’s bigger than space, of course!
Yes, exactly.
I did it!
Ai...
I think you gave those kids too many hints!
We made it too easy for them!
Well you know Doc,
It's pretty dangerous to quiz people
while they're operating a device like a drone.
Besides, the pictures they’re taking with
that thing are serious. Unlike your frivolous quiz.
Yeah, good point...
All three divisions...
Criminal, Public Safety, and Security...
Were scheduled to check the site before the summit.
The public safety division was put in
charge of dealing with the explosion.
That's why Detective Kazami got hurt.
He was outside the building,
so he was only slightly injured,
but the ones who were inside weren’t as lucky.
Hm.
Yeah some people were killed. I saw it on the news.
Yeah...
I guess I’m not supposed to say things like this...
But still, the outcome could have been a lot worse.
I mean, at least no civilians were hurt in the blast.
If the explosion happened during the actual summit,
then the whole world would’ve gone out of control.
That's right. MPD and especially the
Public Safety Bureau are already being bashed.
I guess it can’t be helped since the
accident took place before the summit.
Accident?
Yes. They were going to rule this an accident,
based on the circumstantial evidence
gathered at the site... At first.
And Pops Kogoro’s fingerprints were
also found at the site,weren’t they?
Right.
And when Mr. Kazami found them,
it suddenly became a criminal case.
Detective Kazami did?
Huh?
Thank you, Officer Takagi!
Bye!
Huh..? Be careful out there and get yourself home!
Ran, what's up?
I need your help!
Huh?!
It's dad. They're going to arrest him!
Damn!
I told you! I don't know about it!
Well, we confiscated you computer and we discovered these.
The complete summit schedule.
As well as the blueprints of the
International Conference Hall that was bombed.
Huh?!
No way!
He’d never be able to save documents like
that on his computer! He wouldn't know how!
Yeah, she's right!
He can barely work the thing!
I can't work that stuff.
That's great. You can tell us the rest at the station.
You gotta be joking!
I don't take orders from the Public Safety Division!
All right, then I’ll have to arrest
you for interfering with police duty.
Huh?!
Wait, I barely touched you!
Wait, what are you doing?! Ugh!
Hey!
Oh, no... Please, don't!
4:56 pm, April 28th.
Hey, stop it! Let me go!!
Resisting will only make your charges worse.
Wait!
I'll have your badges! Ugh!
If Pops Kogoro is the perp, what motive
would he have for bombing the Summit Hall?!
I would never do that!
Don't worry. We’ll hear you out during the interrogation.
No... Wait, hey!!
Wait Dad! No!!
Calm yourself, Ran! Call Shinichi now!
I already did!
So where is he...?!
I can't believe he wouldn't show up!
Especially at a time like this!
What kind of person does that?!
Let's go.
You can't do this!
Is this guy Public Safety and Security?
Beats me? How should I know?
His face is injured.
Kind of like yours Mr. Amuro.
Which means you were at the
blast site too. Isn't that correct?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
You were part of the security check beforehand.
And after, you were checking
for possible terrorist activities.
But if you didn't find anything, the
bombing would just be ruled as an accident.
So you figured you’d make a perp up!
Right?!
You’re both police officers,
so you know how a setup works!
You’d also know how to illegally upload those files,
and plant evidence at the site!
Cops wont listen to you if you
don’t have the proof to back it up.
Why would you do something like this?!
I'll tell you why.
There’s something I’ve gotta protect
even if it means risking my own life.
Uh... Ah!
Maybe this time... Amuro's on the other side.
But why?
Why won't you be dad's lawyer?!
Don't tell me that you actually
think that Mr. Mori bombed the place?!
No. He's not capable of such a thing.
Then why won't you help?
It’s unethical for attorneys to defend family members.
A judge could definitely see
that as a conflict of interest,
and dismiss the case before it went to trial.
Put it in simpler terms... If I
choose to be his defense lawyer,
its more than likely it could work against us.
Oh no...
Don't you worry. I'll find us a good lawyer right away.
It's too bad.
It turned out just as you said Mr. Furuya.
If only we'd known earlier...
The members of our Safety and Security
Bureau wouldn’t have had to die...
Yeah, well... I didn't think the place
would get blown up before the summit.
We’re scanning the whole list of known
domestic terrorists as likely suspects,
and of course, the international ones to be thorough.
Any new developments on your end?
I’m checking the communications
that accessed the gas tap at the site.
They’re using a rather unorthodox system.
What do you mean?
As soon as things get rolling we’ll check in
with the Security Police at MPD from our side.
Very good sir.
And, how's the other case going?
Oh, right. We're going to be sending in operative "2291."
Huh...
You still there?
Yeah... Got it.
Can you believe this?
Is it true..?
Hmm...
So in other words...
They found incriminating evidence on his computer.
A digital trail indicating he had
access to the gas line at the site?
Yes... That was the official report.
Straight from the Cyber Crime Division.
So that's it.
Kogoro Mori snuck in here, opened this door,
and rigged the high pressure cable to blow when triggered.
That's impossible!
If that’s the case, then he would’ve
been detected by one of the security cameras.
Not necessarily.
Huh?
The internet’s only been up and
running there since yesterday...
No...
What's he saying in his interrogation?
He's still denying any involvement in the incident,
but we don’t require a confession to prosecute him.
You mean you'd go forward with
this without even a motive?!
With enough proof, we can prosecute.
We're police officers, it's all part of procedure.
Hold on now! Something's not right here!
Something's not right!
Something's not right here, is simply not enough!
Do you think this investigation
will deepen because you have a hunch?
That's too bad...
I see.
Oh, come on!
Why won't anybody take Dad's case?!
Is it too risky?
Probably, that and...
I’m guessing they don’t want to get involved
because it would also be too high profile.
Given that the defendant is the famous Sleeping Kogoro...
Come in.
Hello.
Inspector Shiratori.
I wanted to give you the heads up on
something before they broadcast it on the news.
What is it?
It's Mr. Mori... They're going to prosecute.
Do they have enough evidence to prosecute him?
His fingerprints were found at the crime scene.
On his computer, they found site blueprints,
the summit schedule, and the access
log to all of the incendiary objects.
... That is quite a bit of incriminating evidence.
But why? Why would Dad even...
Mom...
Just wait, Ran.
I give you my word that I'll
save Pops. No matter what it takes!
Doc!
You said you found it?!
Oh good, you're here.
Look.
Looks real.
Yeah, it could pass for a bomb.
I took some screenshots of the debris
from the bombing, like you asked me to.
I fit all the pieces together like a puzzle,
until I had a complete composite picture.
So now in order to specify the type of bomb,
Ai is trying to match it with all kinds
of images found here, on the internet.
Okay.
Finally, I found a match.
Hm?
What is it?
Here come the details.
It’s an IoT pressure cooker?
Yeah, maybe modified somewhat
from a standard pressure cooker.
By setting the temperature and cooking time, you
can make everything from stews, to roasts, to soup...
All from your smartphone, it says.
Cookware?
Besides the pressure cooker,
other items like frying pans, sauce pots,
and even dishes, were scattered everywhere.
Based on those facts, the explosion was
probably in one of the restaurant’s kitchens.
Are you kidding?!
Hm?
It wasn't even a bomb to begin with!
Hey!
You asked her to help figure out what kind
of bomb caused this, and that’s what she did.
So you shouldn’t be talking to
her with that kind of attitude.
This behavior is very unlike you.
I'm sorry, Ai...
What’s wrong? Something happen?
Pops Kogoro...
was just prosecuted...
Huh?!
Who is she?
Wait... What did you just say?
I said, I'm Kyoko Tachibana, and I’ve come
here today to represent the Sleeping Kogoro.
These are all the cases I've handled so far.
Huh... The Extremist Case of Nijoin University,
and... Oh yes, the METI Spy Case!
So, Public Security’s your specialty.
Oh, then you’re the perfect person to handle this case!
But wait, what’s your win/loss record like?
Huh?
Well, that's an interesting question!
I've lost all of them.
Huh?
Well, these sort of cases are very hard to win.
Yes. The cases they indict that are being
won by the prosecution are more than 90%.
And it’s even higher when the
security police are involved…
Basically, there’s no way I can win.
But I’m what they call a “smart lawyer.”
What's that?
She means a freelance lawyer with no office or overhead.
She works exclusively by phone.
Even at a disadvantage I can still take on the work!
That's why you're defending my dad?
You need an attorney, don't you?
I heard about your pending case, and I’d like to help!
I suppose...
Wait, just hang on a second!
We're not done.
She won't work mom!
She can't win! She plans not to!
You have a point.
But I have to say, she already looks incompetent...
So the prosecution may take her lightly...
We can't win that way!
I think we’d be way better off with a public defender...
If we do that, I won’t be able to help!
Huh?
If she takes the job, I can still participate.
Huh...
Even so, she still worries me.
What's it's name?
It's name is Goro!
The police tell me, you're still
denying any involvement in this.
Of course I am, because I am innocent.
But there is a lot of evidence pointing to your guilt.
And it's all right in here.
That's what doesn't make any sense here!
Someone is framing me! I'm certain of it!
Hmm...
Well, from here on out...
The district security police division
will be supervising this bomb case.
Oh my goodness.
Although I don't often handle many
security police cases, I have heard of him.
Is he known for being amazing or something?
Just Like Ms. Kisaki, he’s never lost a single case.
Hehe... He's the complete opposite of me.
Oh! I know all about this one!
It’s the NAZU illegal access case.
Huh? Wait, isn’t that... the space
organization, that's in the United States?
Oh, yes. A game company employee hacked
into its system, just because he could do it.
Kusakabe prosecuted that case too.
And what happened with that one?
The defense lost, of course.
What do you mean, "of course."
Oh man.
Despite everything I’ve already investigated,
I still can’t peg a motive on
Kogoro Mori, and that bothers me...
Hmm...
Motive, huh?
But look at all this evidence here.
We could indict him tomorrow.
Yes, but...
For example, this record saying he
supposedly accessed the gas tap, as you see here,
could also indicate his computer was actually
used by a third party, as a convenient relay point.
Also possible... Someone placed the
blueprint and schedule in his computer,
as a simple way to frame him for this horrible-
Kusakabe.
Honestly...
That’s an emotional, one-sided
deduction which disregards all this proof.
Supervisor Iwai, I will tell the
police to investigate in more detail...
Go indict Kogoro Mori. Just do it.
Please, they're the security police orders.
Understand?
By the "security police" do you mean us, the prosecutors?
Or are you referring to the MPD?
That will be all.
You're dismissed.
... Hmph.
Were you asked to investigate further?
Yes, by Kusakabe.
Then depending on how things
go, maybe Dad won’t be indicted?
No.
Kusakabe asked us to do this for him personally.
The SPD still plan to indict Mr. Mori.
The police aren’t supposed to have jurisdiction over this.
Technically, they should be supervised by the prosecution!
Indictments are a prosecutor’s exclusive authority...
Yes, exactly right.
But, that's only for the civil and criminal divisions.
Besides, the Security Police have...
Well, other circumstances. So, they do things differently.
You understand what I'm saying.
Oh...
Oh, well, you see, there’s a lot involved here...
The MPD, Safety and Security,
and the Prosecutor's department,
all have their own divisions.
The police are supposed to send
what they find to the prosecutor.
The prosecutor takes that and
investigates the case all over again.
As you know, based on whatever the investigation yields,
the prosecution gets to decide
whether to indict a suspect or not.
But, this doesn’t apply to their security division.
Put bluntly, the prosecution’s police
don’t stand a chance against the MPD’s.
They’re outgunned in both number of
investigators, and their skill and experience level.
As a result, the security police
has influence on who’s to be indicted.
Security police influence…
Specifically, when the summit hall was just blown up...
It was as if they had some dirt
thrown right into their faces.
So it’s conceivable that they’d do almost
anything to indict and convict the perpetrator.
Which means, he’ll be indicted then...
Yes, I'm afraid that's right.
No...
Hmm...
It's as if this lawyer wants him to get indicted...
You’re investigating whether Pops' computer’s
been tampered with, by somebody else, right?
Uh, well yes. In fact, Prosecutor
Kusakabe asked us to do an additional search.
Would you mind telling me what you can then?
Shinichi wants to know any information that you may have,
so he can try to save Pops Kogoro.
Kogoro Mori? What’s going on with him?
Mr. Amuro!
Were you listening?
Listening?
I was just concerned about Mr. Mori,
and thought I would bring him
something tasty to eat from Poirot.
Oh,well... Mr. Mori isn’t here anymore.
If he’s indicted, it’s protocol.
He’d be taken right to the detention center.
A procedure you’re familiar with yourself.
Oh, that’s it huh? You sure do know a lot of information.
And remember, that food is
contraband at the detention center!
Right, understood!
What's he after anyway...
2291, succeeded.
Wait... What’s going on here?
Damn!
Hey! Officer!
Wait a sec! I need the laptop you took from Pop's house!
My favorite game is still installed on it! Please!
But that's our official evidence.
Come on!
I can't. Not yet.
Alright, stop it Conan, that is enough!
But it’s a special program that Doc created just for me!
Hmph.
Oh, there you are! I've been trying to get a hold of you.
Huh? Uh...
Oh, I guess my battery must have died.
Can you charge it using that?
Oh! Thanks a lot!
My battery usually lasts much longer...
Uh... So what were you calling me about?
All the case files are gonna be delivered here soon.
She thought it would be good
idea for you to see them, too.
Conan has a real knack for noticing
little details that others miss.
And so if that happens, he can
share them with Shinichi as well.
Right! Shinichi's gonna be the
first person I call for sure!
Thanks Conan, you're the best.
Sorry for the wait.
Here's all the evidence that the prosecutor submitted.
Huh? Does that mean...
That Pops has already been indicted?
No, but we got word from the
prosecutor that he would be indicted soon.
Poor Dad...
Try not to worry. We're going to get him through this.
Please, over there.
Yes, ma'am.
His oral statement, and the investigator’s report.
As well as, pictures of the site taken by forensics.
That's a lot.
Hmm...
There has to be some kind of clue in there...
Damn, there's got to be something...
Huh?
What's the matter?
Uh... I-It's nothing.
It seems familiar...
Looking at this, it's easy to see
how they were able to carry this out.
The details of this police report...
read like a step-by-step criminal's handbook...
A handbook...
Yes, this is Tachibana.
He's in court?
Huh?
Yes.
They're in pre-trial hearings?
Ms. Iwai!
What on earth were you thinking?!
The lawyers knew he was getting indicted, but I didnt!
Must I repeat myself?
The security police make this decision.
First they forcefully decide to indict him and
now they get to determine it’s timing as well?
The court has contacted us.
They said in no uncertain terms,
that tomorrow, we and all the attorneys,
will begin crucial pretrial procedures.
But why did they exclusively
choose to inform to you, Supervisor?
I’m the prosecutor in charge, here!
Let me know when it’s finished. There’s no time to waste.
I can’t find that big container of ice cream!
Oh no...
Oh, I’m gonna go find someone who can help me.
If you don’t mind, you go buy the flour and eggs.
Thanks!
Azusa, you’re gonna make some lucky man a great wife.
Huh?! Are you crazy?
- People can hear you make comments like that! - Huh?
You're really popular with the high
school girls that come into our shop!
The other day, things got heated up with
postings, that I was trying to seduce you!
And of them could be here! You never
know who’s listening to you these days.
Heh, that's true.
Mr. Furuya.
Why do you insist on making a case out of this?
If it’s ruled an accident, we
can’t get a warrant. That's why.
I understand, but the security police shouldn’t
need a warrant to conduct special searches.
Which is why, we’ve got to
leave room for a legal method, too.
We can’t shoot ourselves in the foot.
The illegal procedures that we carry out...
We’ve got to end them ourselves. That's our job.
However, whether we make this whole thing above board,
or whether we cover it up, is
also something we need to take of.
I agree.
But first, we have to determine
which direction is better for us.
For Japan, I mean.
Hey, Mr. Amuro! They only have
the little ice cream containers...
First things first.
Let’s see the evidence. Present your
facts and show me what you’ve gathered.
Then we can proceed accordingly.
Yes, sir.
As you asked, I have an extensive list of evidence.
Ran.
Oh.
Just try to relax.
Okay, but…
The trial isn’t happening for a few more days right?
Right.
It's just the pre-trial procedure.
They have to sort through the issues
and evidence, then they choose the date.
I've told you this.
I know, it's just that...
Miss Kyoko!
Hm?
Ms. Iwai, it's Kusakabe.
We’ve just finished the required pre-trial procedures.
What was evidence that Kusakabe brought in?
It was exactly the same as what we received beforehand.
Here's the list.
And the date of the trial?
It’s been decided, and put into the court schedule.
Ah... I'm sorry but you need to look at this.
I-I'm going to the restroom!
Wait, Miss Kyoko!
The restroom is on the other side!
Miss Kyoko!
Hm...
The wire tap...
The one I rigged Officer Kazami with...
He must be nearby.
I see. Please carry on.
He's here!
Don't tell me that he's inside the courtroom?!
Where is he?!
Huh?!
Is that Miss Kyoko's ringtone?
Yes, is this Miss Kyoko? There’s something
important I’d like to confirm with you.
Oh, I'll be right back.
Why am I hearing her voice coming
from Detective Kazami’s wire tap?
Does she just happen to be standing close to him?
No. The reception's too clear.
They’ve definitely been in
close proximity for some time...
This is no coincidence.
The official report being released by
us the security police, is as follows...
"Nor" was used to illegally access the bomb site.
What's "Nor?"
It’s a browser software that encodes the IP address.
And makes it impossible to trace
by going through several computers.
Isn’t there’s some way you can
manage to unveil the encryption?
Technically no, by design.
Although, if there happens to be a defect
or bug in the structure of NOR’s browser,
it is possible to identify the user.
And additionally,
if we can weaken the perp’s NOR browser’s defenses,
there’s a chance that we could track it.
The entire department is currently
working on it day and night...
To attempt to trace the server, and find the user.
Excuse me.
I have an urgent matter to attend to.
I'm afraid I must go.
Very well.
You're wire tapping that meeting?
Ah...
How'd you know I was here?
When it comes to Kogoro Mori, you sure give it your all.
Or maybe...
This really has more to do with Ran?
Hmph...
Huh?
It's fine. Come out.
I came as fast as I could.
Why'd you call? Mr. Furuya?
Huh... ugh!
And you call yourself a Security Officer.
I-I'm sorry.
But who... How did...?
Hey, wait!
Was it you?
Did you put that bug on me?
No, it can't be.
A child could never.
Toru Amuro...
Is in charge of the security
police nationwide, and it's alias is…
"Zero."
The only ones who can get close to him,
are a handful of detectives,
including the security police.
And you're one of them, aren't you?
Who are you anyway? How do you..?
I'm Conan Edogawa,
and I'm a detective.
The man you keep referring to as Mr. Amuro...
Huh...
... is a murderer.
Huh?!
Last year, he interrogated a
man, who then committed suicide.
Committed suicide?
I'm sorry... This is too serious for a child...
But for some reason, it feels
as if I can talk to you about it.
You sure are a strange one.
Then, as soon as the division
isolates the access point via Nor,
bring in Kogoro Mori...
Hm?
Sorry to barge in!
We have a serious situation going on outside!
Huh?
Huh? Ah!!
Huh? Argh...
Ah! What's happening?!
Mommy, come quick! It's a...
Oh my!
What's happening?!
Woah!
What's going on around here?!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Argh, woah!
Due to the Tokyo summit scheduled for today,
special precautionary measures have been taken,
but a series of inexplicable phenomena has been occurring
Though there is no official announcement yet from the MPD.
Citizens of all participating nations, as well as Japan’s
are voicing their concerns, grievances
and criticisms to the government.
Numerous reports of exploding
electrical devices are pouring in...
Huh? Woah?!
What on earth is happening?
I repeat. MPD has not yet made an official announcement,
Ugh... What is this criminal trying to achieve?
of electronic devices self-destructing.
Electronic devices...
By setting the temperature and cooking time, you
can make everything from stews, to roasts, to soup,
All from your smartphone.
I get it!
The first act of terror was to bomb the summit hall!
What's the latest?
Command headquarters is in utter chaos!
There are over 100 sites that have exploded!
Inside, MPD!
Hey, Conan. I'm sorry, but I can't talk right now.
Inspector Megure! This is all
IoT terrorism! I’m sure of it!
Huh?
What do you mean, IoT terrorism?
Someone’s altering electrical devices into
makeshift bombs, and using the internet to blow them up!
So if you cut off their internet connection
you can make all of this come to an end!
IoT terrorism?
That kid's pretty sharp.
That pressure cooker found at the site,
was probably an IoT appliance, too!
First, the perp was able to unlock the gas tap.
Then he filled the site with gas.
Rigged the IoT device to explode,
and then bombed the summit hall!
No, he couldn't have...
I know.
Pops Kogoro is innocent. He couldn’t have done it.
Really is that the truth?
Huh?!
Hehe, I mean, that’s what Shinichi
asked me to pass on to you, Inspector!
Tell me Conan...
Shinichi's doing everything he can to,
help us, isn't he?
Huh...
Hmph.
Come on.
I'm not doing it just for your Dad. This is for you too.
Interesting.
If what you’re telling me is true then you
may have a decent chance of winning the case.
Yep, because Pops is being detained at the police station,
and he has no internet access there!
No.
Even if one’s being detained, an IoT terror
attack can still be carried out effectively,
if it’s been pre-scheduled.
Huh?
If they identify the access point by tracing the server,
then in their eyes, Mr. Mori is as good as guilty.
That's impossible!
Yeah, but isn’t it kind of hard
for them to trace the server like that?
Can they get that finished before the trial begins?
The security police are doing
it. They wont have a problem.
Hang on...
How are you so sure that the
security police are the ones doing it?
Uh...
Huh? Ah!
Oh! I'm sorry!
Let me explain this to you better.
You see, the security police
often handle tasks of this nature.
This branch of law enforcement, has a
lot of people who collaborate with it.
By people who collaborate, you mean
civilians who assist with police investigations?
That's right.
Especially when it comes to
cases involving targeted servers,
those subject to wire tapping laws.
They use them to collaborate on those type of cases.
If one of them were to look deeper into this,
they may find evidence that
Mr. Mori had accessed the computer.
That is of course to say, if any
such evidence actually even exists!
Oh just leave that, it's broken.
Really? Are you sure?
Yes. I'll probably end up getting a new one.
This doesn't feel right...
There's still something about her.
But I can't put my finger on it...
MPD has officially announced that it is highly likely,
that IoT terror is responsible for the series
of bombings that have recently disrupted the city.
Who’d of expected this would turn out to be an IoT attack…
Of course you did. Who else but
you could’ve figured that out?
Actually, someone else gets the credit for that.
But now we have a credible case.
That’s why I want to get those
side issues wrapped up, ASAP.
And get our "collaborator" off the hook.
Before that, I need to know what intel
Zero has at this point, and how much.
Right.
NAZU?
I’m gonna send all this to the
cyber criminal management division.
We’ll make that department report it at the conference.
Hold on, why should they get the credit for this?
As the security police division, this is our job.
Heh.
It's a reward.
Thanks to them, we can now
investigate these bombings legitimately.
Besides...
The top investigator behind it already knows,
this information came right from Zero.
Hm... You frighten me quite a bit, Mr. Furuya.
Kazami, there are two other men that
should scare you far more than I do.
What's interesting is...
One of them is still just a child.
Hmph, oh yes.
In fact, I know precisely the kid you're talking about.
... Huh?
The latest report reveals,
that traces of illegal digital access
were found originating from Mori’s computer.
Looks like it was used as a relay point after all.
Is any of it traceable?
Unfortunately, the culprit accessed the
system using a burner phone and public wifi.
So, no...
But at that time,
Mr. Mori was in custody at the station,
so obviously it would have been
impossible for him to be at the site.
Also, not only was Nor used as
the relay point in the last case,
it worked so well, it was used again this time.
Ideal for IoT terror.
So it's the same perp after all?
How are we coming along with identifying the server?
Ah, yes... According to cyber crime management intel,
the server is buried, within the NAZU network.
Huh?
Hey! I got here as soon as I could!
Ms. Kuriyama! Thank you for
coming, sorry to ruin your vacation?
That's okay!
How can a legal assistant just sit idly by,
when her boss is going through such a major crisis?
You're so helpful.
Oh, here!
It’s the background check info
that I ran on Kyoko Tachibana.
Huh?
I mean, Shinichi Kudo asked me if
I could do a little digging on her.
Hm? Seriously?
Oh, I see! So that's what he requested...
Why would he ask you to investigate Ms.Tachibana?
Hey, uh...
Huh?
It may seem out of the ordinary, but
I’m sure Shinichi has his reasons for it.
Shall we review the materials?
I found out that last year Ms.Tachibana’s
office clerk had caused an incident.
Huh? But she had told us that she was a “smart lawyer.”
Well, she closed her office last year.
She had to, because a guy named Fumikazu Haba,
one of her assistants at the time,
was arrested for hacking into the
mainframe of a huge game company.
Not long after, Haba committed suicide at the
detention center where he was being detained.
Ah... Suicide?
Uh...
Suicide...
And what does this mean?
We’ve determined that Kogoro Mori’s computer
had been accessed and manipulated by a third party.
And therefore, it’s very unlikely that he is involved.
Okay.
I think we're done.
Yes, but what about the
fingerprints they found at the site?
Ah, the one thing about burned on fingerprints...
Is that they're easily transferred.
Is that what the security police concluded?
Don't indict Kogoro Mori. I mean it.
Your listening to the security police?
Are they making our decisions again?
That is quite enough.
Huh?
Huh?! Ah!
Huh? Prosecutor Iwai?
Yes.
She sustained only minor burns,
but went to the hospital just in case.
So then... Was this IoT terror too?
When we checked her phone,
we actually found it had been accessed via Nor.
Excuse me...
This is Shiratori.
Huh..? What?
That's great news!
Looks like Mr. Mori’s indictment’s been called off!
Huh...
Oh, Mom!
Heheh, great news Ran! I'm so glad!
Mhm, thank you!
I gotta tell Shinichi, Sonoko too!
Heh.
But there's still one more thing.
This is the report from the prosecutor
who interrogated Fumikazu Haba.
Oh, Ms. Iwai, she was just treated for burns.
Her phone caught fire.
She was in charge last year.
Yes.
But now, she's Supervising Prosecutor,
and oversees Mr. Kusakabe, her former colleague.
That's right.
Hm?
As a result of Haba's felony case,
Prosecutor Iwai got herself promoted almost immediately.
And? What's all this about?
Uh...
It looks like you’ve been trying to investigating
me and my former office clerk for some reason.
I, uh...
No, you see, I simply asked Ms. Kuriyama to help me.
It's just a routine background check.
It's extremely thorough.
Congrats on being so efficient too.
Her "too?"
It seems as if you're saying
Mr. Haba was like that as well.
He committed a felony against that game company,
and was the person responsible for
sending your law firm into bankruptcy, right?
It wasn't Fumikazu's fault!
Uh...
It was because...
I couldn't...
Ugh...
It seems like you guys were close.
Not everyone's on a first-name basis with their employees,
but you were.
Are you also aware that he took his own life?
Um... Yes.
At the detention center...
He did it after the security police
got through with their interrogation.
It was very strange.
Last year, he interrogated a
man who then committed suicide.
Why would they do that?
I've never heard of such a thing.
Yeah, well, there were plenty of other
peculiarities that surrounded Fumikazu’s suicide
If I may...
Mr. Haba was a law student for a brief
time until he was dismissed, I believe.
You mean he was studying to become a judge?
Yes,
but however...
during his graduation ceremony from law school...
There was an incident...
Those of you who are aiming to become judges or lawyers,
from today forth should never forget what you...
Head Master!
Huh..?
Why was I..?!
Why was I rejected?!
You have to tell me why!
Calm yourself.
Please tell me!
What was the reason for it?!
Why am I out?!
You shouldn't just kill my chances with no good reason!
Come on!
Please! No!
Let me stay!
I will never forgive you for this!
Never!
His actions were thought to be an
egotistical sence of justice, gone wild.
So he lost his chance of becoming a judge.
The whole legal field was off limits to him,
and he lost hope for any kind of judicial life.
What made you hire Mr. Haba to be your clerk?
I believe everyone has two sides to them.
What you see is only one part of the person.
Your daughter informed me,
that once Mr. Mori is released,
you'll no longer require my services.
I understand.
Uh well, I...
Guess I'll be going as well.
I've still got some work to do.
You're going to investigate the perp's Nor, right?
Right. NAZU's agreed to cooperate with the inquiry.
You mean NAZU, of the United States?
Exactly. NAZU used the Nor software last year,
as part of an illegal access case.
Oh, the one that Miss Kyoko defended.
Because of that very case,
a protocol was developed to track the user,
and it was instated at NAZU.
We're going to have it analyzed starting tomorrow.
Today, they have their hands full overseeing
the critical mission of landing Hakucho safely.
That's the unmanned probe they launched, isnt it?
Yes, and the MPD is panicking, because
that and the Summit are both happening today.
I see. The summit is starting today too...
The public safety division was in
charge of dealing with the explosion.
Put bluntly, the prosecution's police
don't stand a chance against the MPD's.
As a result, the Security Police
has influence on who is to be indicted.
The security police use them to
collaborate on those type of cases.
Miss Kyoko's ringtone?
Why am I hearing her voice coming
from Detective Kazami's wire tap?
The man you keep referring to as Mr. Amuro...
is a murderer.
Haba committed suicide at the detention
center where he was being detained.
Oh! I know all about this one!
It's the NAZU illegal access case.
What do you mean IoT terrorism?
Someone’s using the internet to blow up makeshift bombs!
The details of this police report...
Read like a step-by-step criminal's handbook.
It's nothing...
Seems familiar...
Oh no... It can't be...
Ms. Midori!
Aah!
Please pull up the details of the
NAZU case! Send them to me right away!
Huh?
It's a direct order from Shinichi!
Conan, where are you going?
We were just about to go and
pick up my Dad from MPD right now!
Oh geez...
Why aren’t you answering your phone, Shinichi?!
It seems like you knew I was on my way here.
What I knew, was that something
felt very wrong back there.
Pardon me.
Oh, okay...
I had Doc check it out for me.
And he found a remote control application..
Which as no visible icon.
Where’s your proof that the SP was involved?
There was no proof, as one might expect.
Then why didn’t you delete the app once
you discovered that it was on your phone?
Because I want to confront the perp myself.
You mean to say the terrorist?
Hm... And that's not all.
I figured out the motive.
It involves you and your whole team.
Huh?
It all started with the NAZU illegal access case.
The incident last year.
With Fumikazu Haba?!
Right, and you also knew Mr. Haba committed
suicide while at the detention center.
Yeah... Exactly one year ago today, in fact.
A year ago...
Today?!
I see now... This is terrible...
And I bet, that his revenge hasn't ended yet!
Argh!
Woah!
Huh?!
Ah!
IoT attacks?!
Woah!
Ugh!
Hup!
Mr. Amuro!!
Get going!
Hm.
The unmanned probe Hakucho, is finally
ready to make its return home from space.
Good evening, everyone.
From the National Observatory in Nagano Prefecture.
Oh my, it's getting very late
kids. Why don't we take you home?
What?
But the Hakucho is returning. We wanted to watch!
Please let us stay and watch the broadcast with you!
Can we?
That’s the breaks. Just go watch it at home.
Aw man.
I was looking forward to it...
Hello? Is something the matter?
Well, they told me they wanted to
watch the live satellite broadcast on TV.
Huh? The time between now and it's re-entry..?
Hm?
If I remember correctly its...
Kudo?
Just under an hour from now?!
We gotta hurry!
So it's true, the perp is...
Yeah. He's gonna hack into NAZU and bring the probe down!
But where?!
Damn.
It can't be...
He's gonna do it from space...
Here he comes!
Mr. Mori!
Huh?
Dad you're free!
Yes, I am.
Thank goodness!
Oh!
I know I worried you, I'm sorry.
You did, but you're back!
And Eri... I wanted to thank you for all your help too.
Oh, you don't have to thank me?
I'm so happy for you, yeah.
I apprecaite it, thanks Sonoko!
Oh I almost forgot! I wanted to send a video of
this touching reunion to our other detective friend!
Wait Sonoko, I'm not ready!
Don't worry, it'll only take a second!
Okay, say cheese!
Hm?
Quickly, turn on the emergency lights!
Inspector! Someone has disabled
the emergency backup power!
What the hell?!
What is going on around this place?!
We've got a report from NAZU!
They've confirmed there's been
a security breach of the probe!
Are they sure?!
And now, they may not be able to release the capsule!
The main unit...
will burn up in the atmosphere,
but they've determined the probe's
projected landing position is way off track!
NAZU's in chaos right now!
I'm sending you the new coordinates!
Latitude, 139°- 45' - 08 East in 405 seconds.
NAZU predicts touch down will be...
Can that be right?
Huh?
Uh, this isn't good.
Conan!
This whole time, he was targeting...
the MPD!
It's landing where?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
A 4-meter-long capsule crashing
on us would be catastrophic!
The damage alone would be unimaginable!
Bring in the large van. Start the
process of transporting personnel.
Evacuate everyone within a one-kilometer radius of MPD.
Now!
Yes, sir!
Where's the evacuation map?!
We don't have time!
What's happening?
Don't worry, I'm right here.
Eri, and you too.
Stay real close to me.
Uh... Okay.
It's so romantic!
The probe’s capsule will fall with the
same speed and trajectory as a meteor would!
Meaning, we can only control the orbit for a short time,
before it re-enters our atmosphere!
Within one kilometer of MPD, we’ve
got ministries, parks, and hotels.
We estimate approximately 150,000 evacuees.
To find a shelter big enough for that many people,
we've compiled a list of sites,
one kilometer outside the target zone.
Prime Minister! We were informed by
NAZU that we can't reset the memory!
Why not?!
The signal sent to the probe from the earth station is,
pre-programmed with a specific security code!
If the code doesn't match up...
Then the memory won't be able to be overwritten!
In other words, does that mean
that the perp changed the code?!
That's right! When he illegally hacked into NAZU's system,
and rerouted the probe's entire orbit.
We need him to give us that changed code!
If I can get someone to "collaborate."
The same someone who invents genius things like this.
And have him do what?!
I want Doc to bring the dead back to life!
What a great idea. But then
I'd expect nothing less from you!
I hope we can get him to tell us the code.
I've managed to increase it's
speed capabilities even more!
Doc, the image is still unsteady.
This isn't going to work.
Hm... Well it is my first attempt
at flying this thing at night.
Huh?
A night mission? I wanna do that!
How come only you and Doc get to do it?
Why are you guys here?
The Hakucho! It's not showing on TV anymore!
Well in that case. Maybe you should take over?
I don't quite trust Doc with the controls.
Huh?!
Wow, awesome!!
Hehe, woah!
Very clever of you.
Don't worry, they can handle it.
Now we can start making our preparations.
The three of us are!
The Drone...
Flying Squadron!
Let's go for it!
Now listen up!
Approximately 30,000 people
are evacuating to Edge of Ocean,
near the landfill of Tokyo Bay.
Do you know where that is?
I'm not quite sure...
Excuse me, is that the same place where
they were supposed to hold the summit?
Yes that's right, in fact we're
heading straight to the Casino Tower.
The Casino Tower?
Ah, it's right over there!
Oh yeah... I've gotta contact Shinichi!
NAZU keeps trying to send the code,
but it seems they still haven't
been able to reach the probe.
Damn it!
We've gotta find a way to get that code!
This is the same data from NAZU’s Earth station.
Isn’t that right, mister terrorist?
Ugh... Huh...
Prosecutor Kusakabe, I thought better of you.
What are you talking about?
I should’ve known when I saw your evidence report.
Those shards of glass came from the cooker itself.
It was behind the display window of the control panel.
Which only the bomber could’ve known.
You submitted that as evidence, when the
igniter was thought to be the high-pressure cable.
And that's when your little plan started to unravel.
Ah, nice timing.
The trial documents. These are
from last year's NAZU hacking case.
Which you oversaw.
I see. You got illegal access,
using NOR to cover your tracks.
The same approach you used to pull off this act of terror.
Because it worked so well with the NAZU crime.
... Uh...
But you overlooked one important detail.
NAZU already had a criminal tracking
function embedded in it's system.
When you found out about it, using
NOR to enter and reprogram the system,
you made it look like an IoT terror
attack, and your boss’s phone caught fire.
But it was just a decoy that distracted the police.
That's why the odd timing of the IoT attacks stood out.
Mind your own business!
Damn you!
Hold it!
That phone contains evidence proving that Nor was used!
Oh man!
Not getting away that easy!
Woah... ugh!
Dammit, he's still on the move!
Not a problem! Hup!
Damn you!
Hmph!
Ugh!
Ugh...
Alright, Kusakabe. What was
your motive for doing all this?
Was it to punish the Security Police Force?
If the summit hall gets demolished,
and the probe of the United States comes down over Tokyo,
The Security Police would
completely lose their reputation!
Why? What could you possibly have against them?
As long as you guys continue to be in power,
the prosecution division will
never be able to get anything done!
So you think it's okay to kill
people for the sake of justice?!
I had no intention of killing civilians.
That’s why I bombed the place when only
the staff of the Security Police were there.
And chose IoT terror, to keep the casualties down.
I chose that place to drop
the capsule for the same reason!
You blacked out MPD to give the civilians
who were inside time to evacuate, right?
Yeah.
I get it.
You decided to pull that IoT terror job on your way here,
to scare people into staying away.
Even so, there was still a chance of fatalities!
Of innocent people!
If attaining justice means a
few lives lost, then so be it!
That's the opposite of justice!
Even my...
Own collaborator died...
In the name... of justice...
It was Haba.
Wasn't it? He was your collaborator all along.
But... How did you know?
It was your passcode that gave it away.
Once I heard it, then I knew.
You wanted to keep the keyboard
tones on... So you'd remember.
Fumikazu Haba.Ha ba Fu mi kazu
It was to...
To serve as a reminder of my hatred! Fuel for my revenge!
Each security police collaborator,
gets catalogued first, then they're reported to Zero.
However, the officers themselves
don’t know each other’s collaborators.
I wasn’t even aware that police prosecutors
had collaborators. I just found out last year.
Oh, is that why, you just got rid of my collaborator?!
Wow, that seemed to hit a nerve there.
So what else was behind Mr. Haba's actions?
It was... I requested that Haba do it for me.
I had to know more about the NAZU security breach.
He was the best.
When Haba found out the game
company was harboring the access data,
he hacked in and bypassed security.
He’d retrieved nearly all of it, until...
The collaborators of the Security Police
are willing to carry out illegal
and dangerous investigations...
That’s why the ties between the
us became so bulletproof, so strong.
It’s about loyalty and trust,
far more than its about money.
We’re connected by a sense of mission.
At our core, we’re the same.
Why didn't you say you were my
collaborator, during the interrogation?!
Your whole identity is wrapped up in being a
security police officer. I didn't want to ruin it for you.
You should be thinking about
yourself right now! Not about me!
That's why I was worried about you!
I know too well how injustice feels...
Ugh...
Please! Think about what you're doing here!
This is much bigger than me.
I’d rather be a person who
saves many lives. Not only my own.
Ah....
The aspiration you've always talked
about, is no different than mine.
After that, I told the prosecutor
in charge of his case everything.
Haba is my collaborator.
He had a very good reason for committing the crime.
I don't care, I'm still indicting him.
What?!
Not again... Because of the security police?
Oh relax.
I'll make sure that your name never gets mentioned,
and that the trial will go exactly as we want it to.
That is not what I am talking about!
I decided to go directly to the MPD.
But before I could get there...
Yes?
Haba committed suicide.
What?
We can't be sure why,
but apparently it happened in the detention center.
Right after the JPA's "special" interrogation.
The ones who forced him into suicide...
No, who murdered him! Are the Security Police!!
That’s why you diverted the probe to drop on the MPD?
That’s right. Since the date of Hachuko’s
return was the same one as Haba’s death.
And the IoT attacks?
It wasn't part of the plan...
But as a prosecutor, I couldn't very
well indict an innocent person, could I?
So to prove Kogoro Mori wasn’t guilty,
you decide terrorism was the way to go?
Hm...
But we didn't plan it out... So there
were more casualties than expected.
This madness has got to end right here and now.
Give us the new code you used when you hacked the system!
The Security Police carry out their own brand of justice!
Why should people like Haba have to suffer because of it?!
Quit stalling! Tell us the code!
Go ahead, arrest me! I don't care!
You're not getting any information out of me.
Mr. Kusakabe.
Huh?
Mr. Kusakabe!
It can't be!
How can Haba be alive?
It’s coming live from the MPD heliport.
What's going on here?
It was a security police setup from the beginning.
They framed his death as suicide,
and promised to keep it a secret.
The did this to carefully cover up any evidence
they’d had a collaborator working with them.
What’s more, to ensure the security
police never solicit collaborators again,
that info was hidden from even you.
Wrapping up all your illegal work, without extra help...
isn't something you're capable of.
That is the assesment passed by the security police.
You see...
Haba felt strongly that it was his destiny to be a judge.
He had a very deep sense of purpose.
That’s why when he was dismissed from
law school, and had nowhere else to go
he became your collaborator.
Exactly.
Kusakabe was the one who saved
me from the abyss of hopelessness.
I'd only known him for two years,
but he told me, “Thanks to you, I’ve been able to
do my work as the prosecution of the security police."
Ugh...
That's the only reason why I'm still here.
Please... Mr. Kusakabe, you have
to tell us what the new code is!
If you don’t, there’s a good chance
that Haba will be killed in the process.
How dare you!
Is this this the way the security police does things?!
Its getting closer! Coming through the atmosphere!
Why don’t we have the code yet?!
We’d better get it soon, or we
won’t be able to access the probe!
Mr. Furuya, we're out of time!
Please, we need that code now!
Stop wasting time! Tell us the code!
But if I...
Mr. Kusakabe
Is this the type of justice
that we were fighting together for?
When I broke into the NAZU mainframe,
I reprogrammed the code to be...
A black out?! Are you kidding?!
No sir! Only for about five minutes,
it has to be done for the re-entry!
Yeah but during that time, plasma will be emitted!
Our communications will be disrupted,
and it's questionable whether
we'll be able to revise the orbit!
And, there's a chance the parachute won't deploy!
Aw damn!
Haba, no...
Evacuate him!
Get him out of there now!
Wait, come back!
Did you hear back from Shinichi yet?
I'm still waiting.
But I left him a voicemail?
Jeez, what the hell is he doing?
Conan's not answering either, his phone must be off.
Oh, don't worry about that
little brat, I'm sure he's fine.
Amazing! Look how tall it is.
Come on, this way. Let's go!
Haba! Where are you?!
What is going on..?
Huh?
You're not gonna find him here.
No I saw him... He was streaming from his phone!
You saw a composite image. He's somewhere else.
But he...
The image was captured by a high-powered drone.
We superimposed Haba over a digital
background of the MPD heliport.
He's in a safe place.
Oh, thank goodness...
Mr. Amuro, if they haven't rerouted the probe yet...
Then it's going to end up colliding with...
Of course... A capsule more than 4 meters wide,
will crash down on us at over 10 kilometers per second.
I have an idea. Can you get a hold of
some explosives right now, Mr. Amuro?
Are you thinking of trying to destroy the capsule?
No.
I just need enough blast power to
divert it over the Pacific Ocean.
I like the way your brain works, kid.
You got any better ideas?
Hey Kazami, this is top priority.
That's right, it looks like we may
have to bend the rules a little again.
Of all the munitions we’ve confiscated,
these are easily the most powerful.
You sure they can't track this?
The disposal date is coming up.
We just have to revise the records, no one will know.
Great.
It's up to you now.
Alright, no problem.
I'll send you the probe's projected
course data as soon as possible.
Hmm...
Okay everybody!
It's time for take off!
Alright!
Awesome!
Recalibrate to a new blast site he says.
Now, he says!
Jeez... How am I supposed to do all that!?
Ugh!!
Mitsuhiko... Ayumi...
Genta...
And Ai...
The fate of the country rests in your hands!
Huh? The drone's not flying right!
Maybe don't put too much stuff in it?
We should just leave it somewhere!
D-Don't you dare!
Those are all my possessions! Please!
They’re cherished and precious to me!
Should be okay now, I was able
to narrow down the differential.
I'll send you the image from the drone,
so you adjust the timing on your side.
I got it. Thank you.
I'm not sure but...
Are we allowed to take any pictures of
the Hakucho when we’re this close to it?
It's okay. We got permission from the police.
From the Security Police, that is.
What?!
The parachute's not working?!
No, it appears that the heat
shield is still completely locked!
Prime Minister! Issue the order to destroy it!
No! Wait a second!
What is it?
A strike at this altitude would
only put more lives in danger!
It’s already gone below 30,000 meters.
I got it.
Yes, I understand.
Don't screw this up.
Copy that.
Mr. Amuro!
Will this help you with the timing?
It will.
Hm...
I'm closing in on the capsule!
You can do it guys... You have to!
It's gonna crash if it keeps swerving like this!
Don't worry about it!
It has sensors! If it should fly too close to something,
then it will automatically correct its course to avoid it!
Come on you guys! Don't you want to get a
closer look, and watch the capsule in real time?
I do! I wanna see it!
Yeah, go for it!
Alright, we can do this!
Okay Kudo... Don't get reckless now.
Almost there!
And, go!
Look sir, the parachute!
It's opened up!
What just...
What happened? The screen went dark all of a sudden!
Aw, please tell me that it didn't crash...
You said that it has course
correction built into it right?
Uh well, yes! It does.
I bet the battery died!
Actually, it's not even equipped with that system.
It's okay, it all worked out.
Amazing...
Huh?
Forgive me but... Who are you?
I guess I'd describe us as...
collaborators for a small detective.
Huh?
Yeah. Roger that.
We did it.
That's great!
Mr. Furuya.
We'll take it from here.
Alright.
Wait!
Always remember...
Mr. Kusakabe... We're still one and the same.
I know.
Alright, let's go.
Fumikazu!
Miss Kyoko!
So it's true...
You're alive... I still can't believe it.
Neither can I...
You're terrifying Amuro...
I never thought you were a collaborator...
Much less... For the Security Police!
Miss Kyoko.
Hm?
You were clearly a collaborator as well.
Working for Detective Kazami, right?
You once asked why it was,
that I chose to hire Fumikazu...
You see, he was a disgruntled former law student,
and considered a dangerous entity by the Security Police.
That’s why they asked me to hire him,
they wanted to be able to monitor his actions.
But after only a short time working together...
I started to develop... feelings for him.
And it was mutual for me...
That's the reason, the situation
was even more difficult and painful..
To think you were a collaborator, just like I was...
It all started with the illegal access
of the NAZU computer systems didn’t it?
Yes.
The security police instructed me to rig
the investigation to implicate the suspect.
Around the same time, Haba was caught stealing info,
at the game company that the suspect frequented.
I’ll never understand why he took a crazy risk like that.
Then, I was desperate. I begged
the security police to help him.
They said he killed himself.
I never trusted them after that.
I shut down my law office,
and became a collaborator, waiting
for the right time to retaliate.
And that's when...
you were ordered to take on Pops' pending court case.
To make sure he was found innocent.
Yes.
Although I didn’t know why they were so
hell bent on getting that particular verdict...
But I was set on making him guilty.
Even if you got innocent people in trouble?
I wasn't given a choice!
You see, if I knew that this entire time he was alive,
under Security Police protection?
This would have never happened.
So I suppose now...
Fumikazu's a collaborator for you, isn't he?
What number does he have?
Number?
The SPD assign us a reference
number to identify us anonymously.
My number is 2291.
So what number have you given to him?!
Ms. Tachibana.
You are hereby released from
your duties as a collaborator.
Hear that, Kazami?
Yes, loud and clear. This is our mess, we’ll clean it up.
We keep our word after all.
You can find Haba here.
You're free to go to him at any time.
If you want to see him, we won't interfere with...
I've had enough of this!
Huh...
I cooperated with your scheme of my own volition!
Exactly the same way I chose to betray you!
And nobody made me fall in love with him!
If you think you controlled me...
Then you’re even dumber and more deluded than I thought!
Goodbye...
Kyoko...
She may despise you,
but you've still gotta protect her.
To the end.
That's what we Security Police are about.
We really owe you.
Thanks to all your help, we could
finally bring the terrorist down.
When did you know it was the work of a terrorist?
It's exactly as you deduced.
That day, while we were inspecting
the international conference hall
We saw it was possible that someone
could access the gas valve via the Internet.
We considered the possibility
of a potential terror attack,
and gave instructions out to the
forensics department of the security police.
But upon examining the aftermath,
it could have also been
considered an accidental explosion.
That’s why you had to set someone up as a suspect.
Yeah, we wanted to move him ASAP,
over from MPD security police, to
the prosecution’s police department,
where they had no choice but to listen.
Oh, then that’s why, in order to rule out
the chance of the explosion being accidental,
you sent Kyoko in to defend
Pops and get the charges dropped.
You’re pretty amazing at this
kid. You sure can solve a mystery.
Actually, there’s one more
thing that I haven’t solved yet .
And that is...
Your cellphone.
Huh?
Looks like someone’s trying to get a hold of you.
Huh...
Hey Shinichi?
I’m at the casino tower at the Edge
of Ocean, we've been evacuated here.
Yes?
Call me when you get this message.
What? The capsule?!
An explosion’s thrown the capsule off,
and now it looks like it’s going to
crash onto the landfill at Tokyo Bay!
That’s exactly where Edge of Ocean is! 30,000
people are currently evacuating there for safety!
We can't intercept at this point!
You have plenty of time!
Please! Stay calm everyone!
We guarantee that everyone will get a seat on the busses!
Inspector.
Hm?
There's been a bit of confusion. People are
trying to drive their own cars out of here!
What?!
The only two bridges are totally grid locked.
That's not good.
It's complete chaos.
Shinichi...
Aw, come on! I can't get a hold of Ran!
What do we do? We're running out of time!
Mr. Amuro, looks like you’ll have
to be my collaborator on this one!
Huh?
Hmph.
Bad traffic jam up ahead!
Their evacuation plan's not working!
Hm.
Hmph...
Huh?!
Gah!
There's the Casino Tower...
Mr. Furuya!
Huh?
The capsule's parachute has
detached, and the probe is accelerating!
And?
NAZU has predicted the point of landing!
They say at this rate, it's gonna crash
into the Casino Tower in five minutes!
That's where Ran is!
No! What now? Come on!
Huh?
Mr. Amuro!
Huh?!
Alright, keep yourself strapped in!
What do we do now?!
Huh?!
Hang on!
Woah!
I thought we were finished for sure...
This guy's amazing...
Alright, so what now?
Ah! Wait a sec.
Head for this building under construction!
Huh? I got it!
Okay, stay close to me.
Right.
Things look pretty bad...
Are we gonna make it?
Factoring in the building's height...
and the remaining distance to get to the tower...
We should wait 60 seconds, then floor it!
It's do or die time.
Please make it in time!
Ran!
What is it?
Don't worry, she's gonna be okay.
Ah...
I hope you don't mind if I ask,
but do you have a girlfriend, Mr. Amuro?
Uh... Hm.
Actually,
yes I do.
Heh.
It's my country.
Huh...
We're just about there!
Can you move it? Anything will help!
Just a few more seconds.
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
No good! There's not enough clearance!
That's just great!
Ugh!
Argh!
Now!
Go!
Woah!
Ran!
Mom! Dad!
Woah! Ah!
We'll take it from here.
Now get yourself to some place safe.
The mystery hasn't been solved yet.
Why did you get Pops involved in all of this?
Heh...
Because of my position,
I can't do an open investigation.
So I figured if I got him involved,
you would show up and become my collaborator.
Huh?
With you on the case, we’d be able
to make some progress and get it solved.
Huh...
You're giving me too much credit.
Acting on a personal grudge against the
police for what he considered blatant corruption,
Makoto Kusakabe, a former
prosecutor, has now been identified
as the culprit behind the series of terror attacks.
The security police were cleared of their involvement.
That was probably what they had
decided upon from the beginning.
From inside the capsule of the probe Hakucho,
that was safely retrieved after landing in Tokyo Bay,
Neat!
they collected a sample substance exclusive to
Mars. This could be a groundbreaking new step,
in revealing the mysteries of space.
Hakucho’s launch was a joint venture,
- How cool!
I was hoping we could have watched it with the drone.
Yeah. We could’ve, if it wasn’t
loaded up with all Doc’s things!
Oh right, hehe...
You know something? I don’t think they’re
even aware of what they accomplished here today.
How they were part of retrieving the capsule.
Yeah. What’s more, they saved Japan from catastrophe.
Those guys really are amazing.
Yeah! Now let’s go take out Doc’s
drone! We can check out Mars with it!
That's a great idea!
Yeah, it is!
Doc, make us a new one! Please?
How about you make it bigger this time!
Haha! How could I ever say no to you guys?
Alright!
Yeah... Like that could happen.
We will meet again,
on the ship that floats.
Upon the night sky.