Good morning...
How you doing sunshine?
We're almost out of
shampoo and conditioner
so I'll pick some up on
the way home from work.
Same brand okay with you?
Yeah.
It's crazy how quickly
we go through stuff
when we're together...
It seems like I'm going
to the store every other day.
Mhmm.
So what do you
think we should make
for dinner tonight...?
Is there anything you've
been craving lately?
Not really.
Well... I'll
figure something out
when I go to the store.
You know...
I think it's really fun planning
dinners together with you.
I'm just really happy with
the way things are going.
Takayuki!
What time do you
think you'll be home?
Uhh, ya' know the usual time.
Alright.
Call and let me know
if you gonna be late.
Will do.
Bye... See you tonight.
I'm sure you can't wait.
See you tomorrow.
What now?
Come with me.
Why? What's going...
Mayu and I are starting
to get nervous...
the manager has been acting
very strange around us lately.
The manager.
Yeah, he keeps
following us around
and asking if
we're doing our jobs.
It's creepy.
We were wondering if someone
as dense as you had
seen anything suspicious.
Wow you guys really
cracked this case open.,.
He's watching you two because
you never do your friggin' jobs.
Don't start with me!
Ayu wait!
We're still on the clock.
Save your death blow for later!
I'm wasting my time here. Adios
What is it now?
The way he glares
at the two of us
is different from how he
looks at the other employees.
How?
Oh, I've been going through
the possible scenarios lately.
I think there's something
sinister going on here
like he's thinking lurid
and disgusting thoughts
about us women.
What...? Could that be true...?
I hope he doesn't sell us
to some third world pimp
or make us clean
out the chicken fryer.
Just make sure you
get all the grease off.
Mayu quick...!
Let's take our chances
with the lunch crowd!
Wait for me!
What the hell
was that all about?
Oh, No idea.
Take your seats.
Next stop is
Keyaki General Hospital.
Please press the buzzer
if you wish to stop.
Keyaki.
See ya.
What's up Mr. Boyfriend?
Not much.
You haven't missed
a day in weeks.
Huh, you look like you're tired
or maybe getting
sick or something ...
Remember it's important
for our patient's state
of mind that you
not look depressed ...
If you look happy it
brings their spirits up.
M'kay... I don't
look that bad, do I?
I didn't mean it like that...
But if you have a problem
you can always talk to us...
I could really help
you--suck--it--up!
Sweetie do you know
how dirty that sounded?
That's not what I meant I swear!
I was just talking
about his emotions!
Oh right I'm so sure...
Classic Freudian slip.
You know what I meant to say.
Don't try to turn it around
and make me look like a pervert!
Takayuki please don't take
this the wrong way but...
There you go!
Now go on and show that big
smile to your girlfriend...
Because even if your
life is full of worries
a smile will make
everything seem brighter.
You'd be surprised
at how much quicker
some patients recover when
they have a positive attitude.
Takayuki you're so funny.
I'm serious though,
when they let you out of
here we have to go eat there.
The plates they serve
you are this big!
It's more food
than you can imagine.
I can't wait 'till
they let me out of here.
Whoa, it's later than
I thought it was...
I guess it's time for me
to start heading home.
I've got lots of studying
to do... See you tomorrow?
Aw, really. I was
hoping you'd stay longer.
Come on now.
But don't you like...
spending time
with me... Takayuki?
Of course I do Haruka...
If I could have my way I'd
stay with you all the time.
Really?
Yes, really...
When I'm spending
time with you talking
and having a good laugh
I can forget all of my troubles.
I feel at peace around you.
Wow.
That's very nice, of you to say.
Every moment that
I spend with you is
without a doubt the
happiest point of my day.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
You're welcome.
Well I don't want to
keep you from getting rest...
Soon enough you'll be out
of here and we'll all be able
to go out on the town
like we used to years ago.
Years ago...? Huh?
Whatever you do don't tell her
she's been under
for three years.
Her mind can't comprehend that.
For her, time stopped on
the day she was hit by that car.
Oh sorry. I don't
know what I'm saying.
I've just been so
busy studying lately...
and work is a madhouse.
These last few weeks
have just really flown by.
Haruka?
Takayuki.
I wish we could just
stay like this forever.
So I was at the
store today buying food,
and I completely forgot to buy
the shampoo and conditioner,
I hope that's okay with you.
So, your friend.
She looks pretty intimidating.
Huh...? What friend?
On the bus...
The lady sitting next to you.
Does she work with you?
Oh... That's Ms. Ishida...
She's actually a really cool
person once you get to know her.
I bet...
So you pretty busy
with work right now?
Not really...
It's been kinda slow.
Shall I pour for you dear?
Why thank you.
By the way, I was wondering...
About Haruka.
Uh-huh.
How is she?
What do you mean?
Have there been any changes?
Not really.
She's pretty much the
same as when you saw her.
Oh.
I'm sure she'll be
better soon though.
Is that you, Takayuki?
It's Takayuki!
Mitsuki!
I'm so glad you're
feeling better.
You look great.
Thanks.
Hang in there.
I'm sure you'll be
out of here in no time.
You must get bored having
to stay in this
bed all day long.
Takayuki and
Akane come visit me,
so it's not that bad...
That's nice.
Takayuki takes the time
to visit me every day,
even though he's busy studying.
Yeah?
He even sits with me
in bed... sometimes.
Great.
He is such a
sweetheart Mitsuki...
His funny stories from
work always make me laugh.
You know...
I think I've come to realize
something... that I'm...
I'm in love with him,
and it feels so amazing.
I'm home.
What's going on, baby...?
Is everything okay?
Takayuki.
Yeah, what's up?
Promise that you
won't leave me okay...?
Promise me that we'll
be together forever.
What's going on...?
Did something happen today?
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid you'll leave
the apartment one morning
and never come back.
I just.. I saw Haruka today.
The look in her eyes along
with what she said
really scared me.
What?
Takayuki.
I don't want you
to visit her anymore.
Huh, why is that?
Well, why do you have to?
Look Haruka's parents asked me
to start visiting
her again okay...
They said it would
help her recover
so I said I would
do it for them.
And that's all?
What's that supposed to mean?
You spend more time with her
than you do with me,
all we ever do is
sleep together...
I thought it was,
over between you two.
Over...? What does,
that even mean...?
You know, if I'm not mistaken,
Haruka is your friend too.
You're wrong.
She's not my friend anymore
as far as I'm concerned.
I betrayed her.
Do you still feel
responsible for her accident?
Be honest, do you pity Haruka?
Or do you love her?
Takayuki!
I'll stop seeing her
if that's what you want.
What's up with
Mr. Goody Two Shoes today?
He's usually hurrying
to get out of here by now.
Maybe he's sad.
Yeah... that would
be freaking awesome.
How come?
Because it's sweet payback
for all the crap he's
dealt to us over the years.
Thanks for staying
late Takayuki.
We appreciate the help.
It's... no problem.
I don't have much
going on right now
so I'll be able to work some
extra hours if you need me.
That's good to know son.
What's that all about?
Huh? What do you mean?
Do those two bother you
as much as they do me?
As a matter of fact they do.
So, Is it their
immature attitude
or their laziness
that bothers you?
It's a little of both,
but it's mostly personal.
Why does that
sound strange to you?
No it's just that I don't
think it's very appropriate.
What do you mean?
Well we're at work, for one,
and then there's the
obvious age difference.
No... I think, their
age is almost right on.
Is that so?
Truth is...
Years ago I had a
daughter of my own...
by now she'd be their age.
I miss her every
day that goes by.
Thinking back I wish
I would have spent
more time with her.
It's sad to think
the view outside
her hospital window was all
she had those last few months.
Your total comes to
twenty six hundred yen sir.
And thank you very much
for coming in this evening.
Oh, hey. Are you
going somewhere?
Yeah.
Where...? I thought
you had the day off.
That's why
I bought all this food.
I was going to
make us some dinner.
My manager said he had
extra hours available
if I wanted them.
Since I'm not going
to the hospital anymore
I figured I'd grab
some more shifts.
That is what you wanted right?
Yo! Table three's up!
Fine.
Ayu! It's so busy
my head's starting to spin!
It's just the
dinner rush...
You can't keep
the pathetic cattle
from their daily
gorging now can you?
You better get moving.
Table six looks like they're
about to run out on the check.
Oh, let them. I don't
even care anymore.
Aw, man
Akane?
Wait hold up...
I wonder if something
happened to Haruka?
Yo, jerk ass!
Get back in here already...!
What are you
throwing out the trash
or crying in the
rain like a baby?!
Sky Temple Restaurant.
Yeah sure...
Hold on let me go find him okay?
Takayuki! The phone's for you!
Alright.
Here.
Thanks.
Hi, this is Takayuki.
Can I help you with something?
It's me.
What's going on?
Um, I was just
sitting here and...
Look I think we need to talk.
Mind if I come visit you?
Can't it wait 'till later?
No I...
Where'd that stupid meathead go?
We need his help on
the floor bussing tables.
Takayuki just took a phone call
from some chick then
the next thing I knew
he was headed out of here.
That scumbag!
That's weird.
He usually stops to say 'hi'.
I know.
Takayuki...! You startled me.
I'm sorry, Are you okay?
Of course I'm okay...
What's up?
Why did you come so late?
I was I've been expecting you
since you promised
to come by every day.
I know, it's just...
Is it hard on you?
The entrance exams.
Right. Yeah.
Don't work too hard now.
I'm sure you'll ace those tests.
I really admire all the
time you put into studying.,.
You're going to be
so successful in life.
I'm not much help here,
but I'll be thinking of you,
when you start taking them.
I'll be praying for you.
I'm done.
Would you mind
throwing this away?
Sure.
I felt so alone today...
Thanks for coming to see me.
Takayuki.
I'm so happy, I was afraid
you didn't like me anymore.
Don't be ridiculous...
That's just impossible.
Because I...
Wait... I know what
you're trying to say.
I'm in love with
you too Takayuki.
Haruka.
I'd love it if you
took me to the Festival
when it comes back.
Next time I promise.
It will be just the two of us.
Once you're all better
and the doctors let you out
of here we'll go together...
I'll be waiting for you.
No.
I want you to take
me as soon as possible.
I don't want to wait anymore.
Alright.
I love you.
Is something wrong?
Let's not rush into anything...
I think we should
take our time...
and savor every moment
we have together...
That okay?
Takayuki.
I can't, do this anymore.
They kissed!
I don't believe this!
It's so crazy!
A kiss!
A kiss!!
Rewind.
They kissed!
I still can't believe it!
Yeah I know!
A kiss!
A kiss!!
Kiss!
Kiss!!