I'm outta here.
Oh, by the way,
I can't make it out tonight.
Okay.
Mitsuki... The whole
living together situation.
What should we do about it?
Um, let's just forget about it.
Forget about it...?
But you suggested it
in the first place...
Are you sure about this?
Positive...
I guess I just
got carried away...
Plus, it's not like we're
getting married or anything.
Yeah, okay.
Bye.
A cherry blossom.
I gotta get over
to the hospital.
Hopefully I can make it there
before visiting hours
end for the day...
I'll see ya.
Check it out, sis...
Cherry blossoms.
They're from the tree
in front of the school...
Do you remember that?
If you don't wake up soon,
life will pass you by.
Really...
You're moving at a snail's
pace here, Haruka. Huh...
Weird, it was sunny
just a few minutes ago.
Um, gimme a second.
Oh! This looks good.
Hey, you wanna split
a salad or something?
Oh, or maybe
I could get a reuben.
Afternoon.
Ms. Ishida... You're
here early, aren't you?
Oh, I just had to
pick up some paperwork...
It didn't take me as
long as I had expected.
What are you copying...?
Wait, I thought I told you
we didn't need copies of this.
Oh, you did? I don't remember.
I've noticed you haven't
been yourself, lately...
Is everything okay with you...?
Wanna talk about?
No actually everything
is fine with me...
I just wasn't concentrating...
I'll be more careful.
We need a seafood sampler
and a burger platter.
And can we rush
that order please!
Coming right up!
Hello. Hazawa Trading... Yes.
Yeah... She's right
in front of me.
Is that... for me?
It's your man.
He is your boyfriend...
Calling to check on
you while you're working,
that's usually a good sign that
it's getting pretty serious.
Yeah.
Talk to him like
he's a client...
That way, the others won't know.
Thanks for holding.
Can I help you?
Hey, it's me, babe.
Sorry to call you at work.
I tried your cell, but it
wouldn't go over to voicemail.
I was wondering...
Do you have any plans
for this evening...?
Around six-ish?
No, I'm free.
Cool. I'll meet you at
six at the Station...
Great... I'll call
you later, okay...? Bye.
Gotcha.
Look at that...!
We totally caught
him red-handed!
Excellent work there, Mayu.
How long have you
been standing there?
Well...! 'Hey, it's me, babe'...
Since about the
time you said that!
You know the store rules...
No personal phone calls allowed
on the office phone
during business hours!
What's going on over here?
Oh, just in time, sir.
For what?
We caught...
Mayu and I caught her using
the restaurant's phone
to make a personal call.
That's not true!
So, I guess you fell asleep
at the meeting when
we discussed this.
He's lying, sir...!
The one who made
the phone call is...
No! She did it!
No! Stop blaming it on me!
If you have to
make a personal call
you can always ask me...
But if you lie and
try to hide it, then...
I already told you,
it wasn't me!
Excuse me, sir...
If you don't mind we
have hungry customers
that we need to attend to...
Let's go, Mayu.
I like your attitude, son.
You're gonna pay for this!
Ayu... Was this
call long distance?
No... just forget it.
I hope you step in cat crap!
So what's the plan?
I wanted to look at something.
You said you'd like to find
a place around here, right?
The way I see it,
if we combine our paychecks
we could live in this area.
The most affordable places
seem to be on the south side...
Ooh... not that one.
Okay... It's starting
to get late, sis...
I have to go on home now.
I'm not trying
to forget, Haruka.
It's just that right now we
have ourselves to think about.
I seriously doubt
she would want us
to keep our lives on
hold until she wakes up.
Isn't that right?
Let's focus... on you and me.
So whaddaya say, Mitsuki...?
Let's find a home.
It's okay.
Takayuki...! Takayuki!
Akane! Akane!
Yeah! Woo-hoo!
Well, well...
Check out the speed demon...
Congratulations.
Thanks, but it's nothing...
It was only a
preliminary race...
It didn't mean anything.
Stop trying to be so modest...
I know you worked your
tail off for that race...
You must be exhausted.
Make sure you've
got time to relax...
You don't want to burn out.
Don't worry about me.
Oh I won't, dear...
Sorry I'm probably
bugging you, aren't I?
No. No, you're not
bugging me at all...
So how did
everything go today...?
With Haruka's checkup?
She's doing well...
Physically, she's a
picture of health...
If I could have my
way I would start her
on a rehab program right now
But I guess that's
not a possibility
until she decides to wake up.
Doctor Kozuki!
There you are.
Is there something wrong?
You could say that.
Mister Nagata in room 103 had
his daughter bring him alcohol!
Again? That's the
fourth time this month
this has happened...
You take it easy, Akane.
You too.
Every time we go in his room
he keeps flirting with us.
Yes, one of his more
endearing qualities.
Roll out the red carpet!
You'll never guess
what I did today...!
That's right, I won both of my
heats in the preliminary races.
I wish you could've seen me...
I was so far ahead
of everybody else.
That's strange.
Doctor! Doctor Kozuki!
My sister!
Doctor! Doctor, help!
Thanks for everything.
I'll make sure your next order
has all the Italian
cheese you need.
Have a nice day.
Thanks.
Okay, what's next?
So... Have you made
a final decision yet...?
The apartment?
What?
Oh... No, it's so hard to find
just the right place, you know?
At this rate you
two will split up
by the time you make a decision.
You may be right about that one.
Say, you want to join me
for some dinner tonight?
I know of a great place
with the best gnocchi.
Oh, I'm sorry I can't...
I'm supposed to...
Hang out with him. I understand.
Yeah... How 'bout a rain check?
Here you go, darling.
Watch your tongue.
I made the curry a
little extra spicy tonight.
Hey, what!
You get the octopus from now on.
Huh? Why?!
'Cause your face turns
red when you get angry...
That's why.
How dare you!
See! There!
Jeez, you don't
have to hit me...
I'm just kidding around.
Fine, I know how to take a joke.
You can use my dolphin cup
if it's that important to you...
Come on, the food's
about to get cold...
Start eating, chubs.
Okay.
Let's eat.
Yeah, let's eat.
That's hot!
I warned you.
Don't you like
sweating from hot curry?
Not especially.
Are you gonna answer it?
No, it's probably
just the restaurant...
If I pick up they'll
want me to come in.
Hi, this is Takayuki.
I'm out right now or
I'm asleep or I'm busy.
At any rate,
I can't reach the phone.
Leave a message after the
beep and I'll call you back.
This is way too spicy for me.
Looks like no message.
Oh, you know what...
I bet it was Ayu.
She had to work two shifts today
and she's probably
pissed about it.
This is Akane.
I'm calling with some good news.
You'll be happy to hear it.
I should have phoned earlier,
but I just couldn't
bring myself to do it.
It's... It's my sister.
Haruka has come out of her coma.
She wants to see you, Takayuki.
More than anything.
That's all.
Wait! Akane!
Damn.
Akane?
I'm gonna go home, mom...
Are you gonna stay
here tonight with Haruka?
She's taking a nap right now...
I don't want her to be
alone when she wakes up.
She'll like that.
Oh, Mother...
I just left a message for
Takayuki about Haruka waking up.
I can't go to the hospital.
I can't do it.
Why can't you...?
Haruka is our good friend.
If you decide not
to go and visit her...
you'll regret it every day
for the rest of your life.
I just... I'd hate
to see you go back
to being your
old self, Takayuki.
Let's go there together...
Tomorrow morning.
It's gonna be fine.
Why hello, there.
It's been quite a while
since I've seen you here.
Doctor Kozuki, hello
And you... you're Mitsuki right?
That's right...
It's good to see you again.
Your hair... It looks
different from before.
Oh, yeah. Does it look bad?
Follow me...
I'll show you the way.
Takayuki. What are
you doing nowadays?
I've just been working
part time as a waiter.
Oh, then I guess you gave up
on your entrance exams.
Well, sort of... Yeah.
It's been a few weeks now
since she came out of her coma.
Physically, she's
doing fantastic...
I'll let you in to
see her now, but...
It's very important that
you remember one detail
when talking to her.
What... What is it?
The passage of time...
Don't tell her she's been
under for three years now...
Her mind can't comprehend that.
I don't understand.
Anterograde amnesia.
For her, time stopped on
the day of the accident.
But that's crazy.
I'm counting on you two.
Hey! There you are...
You have visitors...
A few of your friends.
Takayuki.
Haruka, hi.
It's so good to see you...
Thank you for coming.
Um, yeah.
What's the matter...?
You look depressed.
Sorry.
No... Don't be sorry, Takayuki.
If anyone should
be sorry it's me...
I never meant to make
you all worry so much.
Takayuki?
What's the matter...?
Aren't you happy?
Haruka.
It's gonna be okay.
Stop. You're gonna
make me cry, too.
Haruka.
Mitsuki! Thanks for coming.
I'm so glad you're
feeling better, sweetheart.
Thank you, Mitsuki...
Oh no... the children's book
exhibit is over by now.
There's supposed to be
another exhibit in a month...
By then...
Second semester
will have started
and I'll be so busy studying
for the entrance exams
that I probably
won't be able to go.
We were supposed to go
together, Takayuki...
Sorry I couldn't make our date.
Oh, don't worry about it.
It's no big deal.
There'll be another one this
summer once school's over.
Then you'll have all
the time in the world
to go check out the exhibit...
And if you don't want
to wait that long,
I'm sure you can find
a break this semester...
Right, Big Brother?
Uh, yeah.
But I...
Your sister's right, Haruka.
There will be plenty of
chances to go next time.
What's most
important right now...
is for you to make
a full recovery.
Mistuki, hello...
Thanks for coming by.
You're such a good friend to me.
Alright.
It's time to take your
temperature, Haruka.
You're a bit feverish...
You must be exhausted...
I'm sorry, but...
I think it's about time
for you guys to go.
Why don't you lie down and rest?
I'll lower the bed
for you... There you go.
Are you okay?
We need to talk.
Takayuki, why did
you have to come
to the hospital with Mitsuki...?
Seriously, what was
the point of bringing her
into my sister's room with you?
Akane.
And why are you even here...?
Was it just so you
could show my sister
how close you are
to her boyfriend?
I can't believe you'd come here
and act like you give a
crap about her! I hate you!
Akane!
It's okay, Takayuki.
But...
It's all right... I'm fine.
You guys make me sick...
You ignore my sister
for three entire years
when she was in a coma,
and the whole time
you were hooking up with
each other behind her back!
Akane, please listen.
I don't wanna hear it!
My sister's best
friend betrayed her...
How could you do that...?
Tell me... Aren't you
ashamed of yourself...?
Do you feel any guilt at all?
I'm sorry.
Takayuki.
My sister needs you now.
She wants you to be by her side.
Yet you just stand there with
that stupid look on your face.
You're nothing but a coward.
Are you really gonna
go through with it, Ayu?
Of course I am.
Why should she get
the most attention
when all she does
is sleep all day...
You ready?
Right behind ya.
Here we go!
Quick run!
Right away!
What's up?
I am.