No way! Seriously?!
I'm totally serious!
Here we are swimming
our butts off
during a pivotal meet
and there's our coach
snoring away like
my asthmatic grandpa!
I can't believe he did that.
Yeah, neither can I!
Look out!
Hey, Mitsuki...!
What's going on,
ya human dolphin?
Akane!
Geez, sis. Was that necessary?
You really scared me.
So I wanted to tell you
something, Mitsuki...
I made some modifications to
my upstroke over the weekend.
Uh...? Your upstroke?
I watched the video of you
from last week's meet
and analyzed it myself.
Video?
Yeah, I love the way your
arms glide over the surface.
It's not only graceful
it's the key to winning.
Your form is just so perfect...
With that image
burned into my memory,
nothing can stop
me from dominating!
Huh, where'd you see this video?
I didn't know
someone had taped me.
Well my sister had the video
camera out and I just...
I told you not to tell!
Oops! Sorry.
Geez, thanks a lot ...
Didn't I tell you
how embarrassed
I get when I'm on tape?
Akane was so insistent about it.
She wouldn't let it go.
Then I asked the coach if it
would be okay and he... Sorry.
Oh well...
I guess you can kiss
our friendship goodbye.
Fine then, see if I care.
Okay... sis, Mitsuki...
I'm sorry... I never...
I never... intended...
for you guys...
to fight about this.
Akane...
You totally fell for it!
I don't think it's
possible for Haruka
and I to fight about anything.
We were just messing with ya.
Huh?
You guys suck!
Oh come on,
can't you take a joke?
Mitsuki!
What are you doing?
We have to go.
I'm coming.
What a gorgeous day.
Akane.
Yeah? Do you need me
to get you something?
I hope Takayuki visits today...
I miss him.
You think he'll come?
I don't know if he'll make it.
He's gotta study for his
entrance exams, remember?
Yeah, I know that...
It would just nice
if he came to visit.
Oh, I almost forgot...
I need to change out the water
for the flowers before
they start to wilt...
I'll be back.
So are you...
still gonna visit her?
Yeah.
Oh.
I just feel... obligated to her.
So when she
recovers completely...
I was wondering...
if you were gonna fill her
in on our relationship?
Yeah I... plan to.
Alright... I was just...
Everything's gonna
turn out okay, right?
I happened to walk past school
during a sales call today.
Peeked inside and
I barely recognized it.
Everything is changing
so much right before our eyes...
So much has happened recently...
So much it's hard
to keep up with.
I can't even begin to
wrap my brain around it.
That's funny,
because I feel the same.
I'm so happy
I have you, Takayuki.
You're all I've got.
It's gonna be alright.
Baby.
We're gonna get through this.
I love you... so much.
People can be so
gross sometimes...
I'll just pretend
I didn't see this.
I wish this place would
open their pockets
and hire a busser to
do this crappy job...
But no they're too cheap.
Hey... let... go of me!
Where do you think you're going?
I'm gonna go wherever
my feet take me!
Your feet can take
you wherever you want,
but only after you
clear table three. Got it?
Why don't you
clear it yourself?!
Okay then... Come with me.
What are you doing?
Stop torturing me!
You want me to
do it myself, huh?
Why should I do that?
You haven't cleared
one table all day!
Let go of me!
Now clear table three.
Over my dead body.
Be careful there, Takayuki...
You don't wanna pull
her face off.
If that's what it takes to
get her to work then so be it.
Shut up!
Takayuki?
Yes, sir?
I see that you're
working hard today.
Oh right.
Sorry.
I wanted to talk to
you about something
if you can spare a minute.
I asked Mayu to
clear some tables,
but I guess that's
too much for her...
Ayu, you're obviously
not doing anything.
Would you help your
friend at table three?
Huh?
I said, would you please
clear table three with Mayu?
Yeah, yeah.
You heard the man,
take care of table three!
Listen... don't push me...
or you'll get a stinky
gift from my cat.
Take care of table three.
Cram it!
So, what was it you
wanted to talk to me about?
Right, Chen just called in sick,
so we're gonna be understaffed
for the dinner rush...
I was hoping you'd be
able to work a double.
Tonight?
Yeah, can ya help me out?
Sorry, but tonight's
no good. I have plans.
Plans? He wishes.
Do it. I dare ya.
Hey, you filthy bum loser...!
Why don't ya put in
some decent hours of work!
Speak for yourself, you slacker!
Man.
Takayuki.
Why don't you
just take the plunge
and start working
full time here...?
Everybody knows
you're the only one
that can handle
that lazy, little brat.
Well look who's
here... Takayuki.
Hello.
I guess I'll see you
in the morning then.
Fine.
Stop wasting your time here.
Is something the matter?
No everything's fine...
How's Haruka doing today?
Well... Physically
she's doing fine.
What about her memory?
That's going to take
some time, unfortunately...
However she does remember that
you visited her a few days ago.
That's good... isn't it?
Haruka.
Takayuki, hi!
I wanted to see you.
So how are you feeling?
Um... Okay... the days
seem to go by quickly ...
I thought it was
morning a minute ago
and then the next thing
I know the sun is going down.
Soon it will be nighttime,
then in a blink of an eye,...
It'll be morning again...
It's kinda... scary.
You're so very warm...
and reassuring.
Haruka, I was wondering...
Hey... let's make our wish.
You remember?
Like the brightest stars
in the darkest skies of night.
Hearts that have truly
joined will never fade.
Haruka...
Haruka... Let's focus on
you getting better first.
It's scary... the days
go by so quickly now.
We wanted to
thank you, Takayuki...
I didn't think you would ever
want to visit Haruka again.
You're so kind, Takayuki.
If it's alright with you...
we'd like you to
continue visiting Haruka...
It seems like whenever
she talks it's always
about how great you
are and how much...
she misses you.
The doctor said
her memory lapses
will start to decrease...
but in order for
that to happen...
This isn't easy for me,
but I'd like to apologize for
the way I treated you before...
I know I asked you
not to ever visit again.
Our daughter...
she really needs your
support right now, son.
More than you know.
So please continue seeing her.
Whatever time you
can spare would be fine.
Please.
I'll visit her every day
until she wakes up.
I promise. It's the
least I can do for her.
Haruka's the most
important person in my life.
Or she was, then.
Hey, sweetheart!
Hey, babe.
That was really good.
Thank you for cooking.
Huh...? Oh, thanks...
Glad you liked it...
How 'bout some tea?
Sure.
So tell me how it went.
Is Haruka okay?
I think she's doing
pretty well considering.
Was she able to remember
that it was your second visit?
Yeah... I guess
you could say that.
That's a step in
the right direction...
What about me?
Oh, of course she
remembered you, sweetie...
As a matter of fact,
she asked why you weren't
there to visit with me.
Oh.
Here you go, babe.
Oh, thanks.
By the way... don't you
have to get home soon...?
You have an early
start tomorrow, right?
I'll walk you home if you want.
I was planning on
staying the night here.
Okay, yeah. That's cool.
'Kay then.
That teacher's boring as hell.
Tell me about it.
Takayuki!
Yo, Shinji!
Sorry you had to come
all the way over here.
It's hard to get away with all
these classes during the day.
Don't sweat it, man.
I'm not doing
anything important.
So no work today?
I'm off.
Sweet.
Hey, Miki! Over here!
You going to Philosophy today?
Yeah, probably.
Awesome. I'll see you there.
Damn, she's cute, man...
Is that the girl you
were telling me about
the last time we hung out?
Yeah!
Is she the one who stood
you up on Saturday night?
Yeah.
You think she likes you?
Of course she does!
I mean... I hope that she does.
If you really like her...
then go for it.
That sucks.
So I guess she's far from
a full recovery, huh?
Yeah.
So are you still gonna
go visit her, like before?
I feel it's my
responsibility to.
Is it just a
responsibility you feel?
Or are you still
in love with her?
No, I'm not.
You sure about that?
Yes.
Then good...
Just don't betray
Mitsuki, okay...?
You have something
really great going
with her and you
don't wanna screw it up.
I know that.
This must be hard on you, bro,
but try to smile when
you're around Mitsuki.
Right.
So, uh, tell me...
Do you love her?
Yeah, very much.
Hazawa Trading, can I help you?
Hi, Hiro.
Did you happen to get those
contracts I faxed you...?
Right... I need it
initialed on the first page
and signed on the last...
Great. I'll be looking for
it by the end of the day.
Look who it is.
The backstabbing bitch.
Akane, look...
My sister's resting now
so she can't take any guests.
I see.
I can't believe you have
the nerve to show up here...
especially after what I said.
Actually that's what
I wanted to talk to you about.
Oh really?
Well, if it's about Takayuki
I don't want to hear it.
So don't bother.
It's okay if you don't
understand everything.
I was just hoping I could be
a hundred percent
honest with you.
I don't believe you.
You think you can just walk
between the raindrops...?
You can't just say
whatever you want
and be rid of the
guilt and the pain.
You're not getting
off that easy!
I never knew a human
being could be so selfish!
But you're wrong...
I'm not a selfish person--
Get out of my sight!
And don't come back
until you've really felt
what it's like to suffer.
Now leave before
I call security!
I said get out of here!
Akane?
What's going on? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You really don't know
when to quit do you?
Why come here when you have
no feelings for her...?
I don't get it.
Takayuki.
Hi, Takayuki.
It's about time you showed up.
Look, it's the boyfriend.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to interrupt you guys.
I'll wait outside
until you're done.
Actually we just finished now...
You have good timing.
Haruka's doing especially
well this evening.
Isn't that right, dear?
I am.
Buh-bye.
See you later, boyfriend.
Take good care of her, please.
Takayuki?
Come over here by me.
And don't come back
until you've really felt
what it's like to suffer.
What?
No, I didn't! That's not true.
That's not what I heard.
Mitsuki told me so.
She said that you wore
cute boots to gym class
even though the teacher
told you not to.
I can't believe she told you...
She promised me she
would keep it a secret.
So you really did run
the fifty-meter dash
in crocodile skin boots?
I only did it because
it had rained that morning.
Didn't you have running
shoes in your locker
that you could've changed into?
There wasn't any
time to change...
Stop teasing me already.
You're starting to embarrass me.
You know this story
was quite famous
back in high school...
I never would have imagined
that it was you
who did it though.
Takayuki, please
stop laughing at me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
But...
I'm happy...
I love to watch you smile.
It makes me feel so good.
Haruka.
Are you still studying
for the entrance exams...?
Any progress?
Um, yeah... Slowly, but surely.
Huh... I would like
to start studying soon
just to get my brain working.
I'm starting to get anxious
being stuck in this
bed all the time.
You'll be fine.
You just have to be patient.
It's important that your
body fully heals first.
Yeah... I understand...
I'm really glad you could
come and hang out with me.
Would you like to do
the wish together again?
Uh, sure.
Say it with me?
Did you forget it?
No.
Is something wrong...? You okay?
Alright... I'm ready
to go when you are.
Like the brightest stars in
the darkest skies of night...
Hearts that have truly
joined will never fade.
Even if these hands
ever pull apart...
The connection between
us will never be betrayed.
It's gonna be alright.
Like the brightest stars in the
darkest skies of night...
Like the brightest stars in
the darkest skies of night...
Hearts that have truly
joined will never fade.
Even, if these hands
ever pull apart...
We will not forget the
love we have in our lives.
May the stars in the sky...
Shine bright forever.