Isn't the sunlight sparkling
on the waves beautiful?
Yeah.
I love this time
of day. Don't you?
Yeah.
Did Mitsuki... come to see you?
Uh-huh.
What happened?
I slapped her...
I was so upset.
I'm sorry.
Haruka!
I'm okay.
I'll be fine. I can do this.
You can't...
It's too soon for this.
I always thought
no matter what happened
to us we'd always
remain friends.
And if anything came between
us it'd work itself out.
It won't...
I know it's impossible.
I... love Mitsuki.
She stayed by my side
when I was ready
to give up on myself.
And because she was
there to pick me up,
I can be here with you.
She suffered
through all of this,
as much as any of us.
But to her, I was
somewhere else all the time.
My heart was never
with her the way
she deserved it to be.
In the end, she had no choice
but to question
why she was with me.
Why she was even around.
And I... I never
noticed her pain.
Like it was the
suffering of a stranger...
I never even noticed.
Until the second
that she left me...
Then it was the only
thing I could see at all.
I owe her.
If she's in pain, it's my
responsibility to heal it.
No matter how long it takes.
Three years was how long it took
for my whole world to change.
But time can't be taken back.
For three years,
you lived a life
that I can't begin to know.
I've searched for the
Takayuki I used to love.
The gentle boy that
I knew in high school.
But he doesn't exist anymore...
He just vanished... Gone...
While I was asleep...
gone forever.
I can't apologize enough
for putting you through this.
But I don't regret any of it.
I don't want to ever
forget what we've seen.
It's been... lovely... a dream.
Thank you.
Once upon a time,
Mayal the fairy lost her memory.
It simply washed away,
and she had to live
in the forest all alone.
Until one day,
a girl discovered her hiding
in the bushes, and
the two became friends.
The girl called her
other friends over
and they played with Mayal
all day and into the night.
They played all Spring, all
Summer, and into the Autumn.
But Mayal was not
like the others.
She aged differently
from her new friends.
As the seasons passed on,
Mayal's friends began to mature
and grow quicker than her.
They seemed to
forget about Mayal,
leaving her behind.
In the end,
her one last friend was
the very first girl
she had met so long ago.
However, this girl
had also grown up
and knew she
could no longer play
with Mayal the way she used to.
So one day, she came
back to the forest.
Seeing her...
And seeing the deep
sadness in her eyes...
Mayal decided
to give her a gift.
What did she give her?
The gift of parting words.
At that time, humans
had no words of parting.
And Mayal was a parting fairy.
During the turmoil
of losing her memory,
her purpose was lost to her.
This was why she
felt she was always
saying goodbye to
whomever she knew.
The girl who had become an adult
heard these words
of parting from Mayal.
After learning
these special words...
the girl went home...
she became the world's
kindest person...
knowing these words.
That's what brought
you and I together.
The story of Mayal's Gift.
Takayuki. I want us
to part with a smile.
'Kay?
Goodbye.
You can't do that!!
What do you mean,
you're just taking
the day off...?!
I'm not gonna let you off
without you giving me
a good excuse for this!
He hung up on me!
I, uh...
She resigned last week.
I don't understand. Why?
Don't tell me you haven't even
spoken to her about this?
No, I haven't... Where is she?
I figured you would
be the one to know.
Ask yourself, where do you think
she would go at
a time like this?
What do you think
I've been doing...?!
I'm looking everywhere.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to say to her
if you do find her?
Do you know?
Or are you just running
around, without a plan?
With the person you are,
what can you offer her?
I don't know...
But I... I just,
I have to see her again!
Then I can tell her...
You're so naïve... You and
Mitsuki both.
And I'm...
a bit jealous of that.
Hello?
Yeah...
Hi, there, boss... Huh...
So they want me to come down
to the head office
this afternoon?
Right.
I'm very sorry.
I almost don't
know how to say it,
but I have to turn
down the promotion.
You see...
There's someone
very special to me...
And I've hurt her in ways
I never imagined I could...
So now... I have to find her...
And make things right.
I understand.
You can't lose a woman like her.
They don't come around
that often. Trust me.
Thank you.
Hey, man. Have you
talked to Mitsuki...?
Just let me know if you have...
Or just tell me
when she calls you...
Can you do that? Please!
Sure, man.
Love-struck idiot.
Well, I'm here.
You wait long?
Nah.
Please, Mitsuki...
Where are you?
Takayuki...
Mitsuki...
No!
Please... Let me go.
I'm fine...
Without you, I'm fine.
I can manage on my own.
From now on,
I won't have any
problem being alone.
Well, I will... I need you.
I need you... with me.
That's all I want.
I'm not gonna be
anyone's replacement.
You know that.
Listen, you're
not a replacement.
You're not...
I love you, Mitsuki.
And Haruka...?
What happens to her?
It's over. For good.
She's out of my life.
We've said our goodbyes.
I won't ever see her again.
It's too late for us...
I've already moved
on with my life...
I don't ever wanna go back
to being the mess
that I was before.
Listen, when my life had
gotten so out of control...
You came along
and picked me up...
You have always
been there for me,
Mitsuki, no matter what...
That's why...
I want you to stay...
I need you to.
I don't know if
things will work out,
but I can't think of a
life without you in it.
I want to be with you.
I've missed you...
No going back...
We start from here.
Congratulations, Haruka.
We're all proud of you.
Thank you all so much.
Hotaru would have loved,
to see Haruka walk out of here.
Yeah...
Yes! What a wonderful day!
Single men, watch your backs.
You're moving in today?
I'm proud of you.
I'm sure you'll be quite happy.
Hold on a sec...
Someone else wants to say 'hi'.
Hey, Takayuki is that you?
It's Mayu!
The restaurant just isn't
the same without you...
Please come back to work soon.
Ayu and I miss you so much!
Hey, dog face!!!
Let the record show that she
was speaking for herself there!
Contrary to what Mayu said,
I'm glad you're gone
and I hope you stay gone!
Because scum like
you doesn't deserve
to work in a place like this!
I didn't say bye.
Trust me you didn't
wanna say goodbye
to that jerk anyway.
Now let's get back to work...
The new blood needs
our help on the floor.
Okay! Whatever you say, Ayu!
Here you go.
Thanks. I've been
waiting for this.
This is fantastic work...
Let's get together again
in the next few weeks
to discuss your next project.
Okay. I have a lot
of good ideas to share.
I'm looking forward
to hearing them.
Take care, Haruka.
I'll see you soon.
Excuse me, miss...
Can I get a fruit cup and
a tea over here, please?
Hey, you.
You're here early.
Well I got out of
training camp early today...
So here I am...
Man, I'm thirsty.
Really.
Now. Please,
tell me everything...
You get your manuscript back?
Yup.
Wow! Awesome!
Sis, I'm so proud of you!
Thank you.
Do you mind if I read it?
I can hardly wait.
Don't... Give... Up...
Haru the tiny ermine spends
yet another endless day
climbing up the hill
with gritty determination.
Don't... Give... Up...
Haru had finally
found the treasure,
and with it, she now had the
faith she had been looking for.
The faith that one day,
all of her dearest friends
from the past would join
together to share a cozy nap.
And that is why,
once again, she pushes
her little body towards
the top of the big hill.
Don't... Give... Up...
That is how Haru
found her True Treasure.