Man, it's pouring again.
It seems like it's
never gonna stop.
You spend more time with
her than you do with me.
All we ever do
is sleep together...
Takayuki...? Takayuki?
What's wrong?
Is there something
bothering you?
Oh. The doctor
said real books'd be
too much for me...
Can you believe that...?
She said that all the big
words would just tire me out...
So mom bought these
for me to pass the time.
Well that was nice of her...
But... I thought children's
books were your favorite.
They are, but mom can't
find my very favorite.
She's looked everywhere.
Oh really... Which one's that?
The one that you
loved--Mayal's Gift?
Oh, right. How could I forget?
Well... mom can't
find it anywhere.
Maybe I should
try looking for it.
It's worth a shot.
Really?
Of course...
I would do anything for you.
That's awesome. Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
♪ Little lost doll...
Little lost doll... ♪
♪ Where have you gone? ♪
♪ What is your story? ♪
♪ When will you be found. ♪
♪ Little lost doll...
Little lost doll... ♪
♪ Come back to me. ♪
♪ Come back to me soon. ♪
♪ That's where you belong. ♪
♪ Come back, come back.
Come back home. ♪
You're back. I was worried.
It must be raining
pretty hard out there.
Um, if you're hungry...
I could heat the dinner I made.
It's really nothing fancy...
Just some noodles and stuff,
but it should warm
you up a little.
I'm sorry I called you
at work like that...
Sometimes a girl just needs
to hear her man's voice...
I was just feeling
a little lonely I guess.
It's fine.
I'm gonna jump in
the shower for a minute.
After walking in that cold
rain, I wouldn't blame you.
I put some fresh
towels in the cabinet...
You want me to heat up the
food while you're in there?
Don't worry about it.
Come on...
It's just that you're supposed
to get up early tomorrow,
so you should go to bed now.
Here it is!
This is it...
but it's just so beat up
and ragged looking.
Pardon me.
I heard a crash! Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks, Mayu...
I just kinda... I klutzed out.
There's blood on your hand!
What?
Bandage, we need
a bandage, STAT!
Oh, it's just a little cut.
I'll help you!
I'll be right back
with assistance!
Get up slacker.
Why can't you do your job
without causing so
many problems for us?
You're right, Ayu...
You don't have to
worry about a thing...
I'll clean up the mess myself.
Duh... What did you think...?
That I was gonna help you
clean your mess up...?
Besides if you haven't noticed,
I'm on my lunch break.
Good for you.
You know...
You'd better get your
head out of the clouds.
You have too much
work this afternoon.
Excuse me.
Yes, ma'am?!
With these stupid customers,
I'll never get to
my stupid lunch.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of your
customer once I'm done...
Go ahead and eat
your lunch, okay.
What did you say?!
For whatever reason,
we've been slammed
since breakfast...
You've earned your break,
now go take it.
Could I get some
service, please?
I'll be right with you.
Mayu is here to save the day...
here's your bandage...
Hey, Ayu... Where's uh...
Where did Takayuki run off to?
He needs my help.
Shrimp scampi...
and a bottled water.
We'll make the delivery date
to your store the
fifteenth of next month.
Sounds like I made a good deal.
Thank you so much.
I look forward
to working with you.
Uh, Mitsuki?
Oh, yes?
You zoned out again.
Yeah, sorry.
Have you not been getting
enough sleep these days?
Look, if there's anything
you need to talk about...
Just know I can
be your friend...
as well as your boss, okay?
Excuse me for a sec.
What...!
Look, just talk to
the damn lawyer, okay!
For crying out loud,
you can have the car...
No, I don't care.
I just want this over with.
Sorry, guys.
I'm so tired.
It's about time.
You know the last one here
has to pay for everybody.
That's not fair.
Where'd she go?
You guys remember the time
when Takayuki fell off the--
Oh, please, let's not
bring that up again.
I want those days...
to come back.
Yo, what's up?
Hi, Shinji?
Hey...
Mitsuki, what's going on...?
You get a break from work?
I just wanted to
hear your voice.
Hey, is there something wrong??
No, not really.
Did you have a fight
with Takayuki again?
I guess you could say that.
If you want me to kick his butt,
you know I'm always
willing and able for that...
Or I could just call him for
you, and try to explain things.
No, I don't want that.
I just, well,
I don't even know...
Come on, what is it?
Nothing.
Do you want me to come by?
You still there?
Yah!
Miki, don't do that...
You could give me
a heart attack...
And I'm too young to die.
Yeah, right...
Oh, sorry I didn't
see you on the phone.
Oh, yeah.
Well I was.
♪ Little lost doll...
Little lost doll... ♪
♪ Come back to me? ♪
♪ Come back to me soon.
That's where you belong. ♪
I finished clearing
off table three.
It's absolutely spotless...
Well, well...
I'd say you're a little
behind here, Takayuki.
Yeah, thanks for noticing...
Just leave them anywhere.
I'll get to them.
I would but there's
no more room...
They'd just fall to the ground.
Hey, you want me
to help out here?
I got some time.
Nope, I can manage.
'Kay.
What the heck...?!
Where's the dishwasher?
Takayuki?
Yes, sir?
You have a minute?
Of course.
I wonder what that's about.
He's probably getting fired.
Mr. Ito, hi.
Hello, Takayuki...
It's nice to see you.
Thank you very much, sir.
I have something...
I hope you think
it's a fair offer...
But let me know if you don't.
What kind of offer?
A contract?
Yes, for full time...
I'm sure you have a good reason
for only working part-time,
but you are valuable.
You're a hard worker
and personable.
And I promise your work
load won't change too much.
Take your time and
consider your options...
Go home; talk it over
with your girlfriend...
Then just let us
know what you think.
Manager?
Yes.
You'll be making more money,
which is always good...
and you're due for
something like this,
at least that's what
your boss tells us.
Mr. Ito, please.
I'm sorry, did
I blow your cover?
Hear anything?
I just hear the door.
I wish they'd speak up.
They're way too quiet.
What do you think
that means, Ayu?
They're either rats or thieves.
So that means...
They're like three
blind mice, but thieves!
What?
Oh... What're ya doing?
Just minding our own business!
What's up with them?
I don't ever know.
It could be anything.
I know we're busy out there...
Then I'll get back to work.
Do I really have time
to think about this offer...?
I mean, I don't wanna
let it go too long.
Yeah.
What kind of offer?
Do you mind...
if I head out just
a little early today...?
I need to talk with
Mitsuki about this...
Thanks for covering for me.
I'm sorry for
leaving you like I did.
Don't worry yourself about it.
I understand you have a
lot you're going through...
Everyone needs a little break.
Thank you.
It's Shinji.
I'm trying to find a
better copy of this book.
I'm sorry. That's
a fairly rare book.
We just don't carry
anything like that.
I'm gonna have to get
a whole different list
of bookstores to check out.
Ayu...
We're not even at work.
What do you want from me?
What's this about an offer?
You were eavesdropping?
Yeah, so what?
What about the offer?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
It's none of your business!
Just let it go!
Hey, give that back!
What...?
Why'd you buy such
a torn up book...?
You broke?
Shut up, Ayu!
You don't know!!
Give it back...! You idiot...
Someone very special to me
needs a copy of this book,
but I can't give her this one.
Now get outta my way!
Look! Wait up!
I said move!
Why can't you give
her the one you have?
Because I can't give her a
book that looks like this.
Well, why don't you
just get a new one?
I need it to be
older than three years.
Three years?
Fine... No sweat...
Just let me see the book.
Hello, it's me...
I need a favor.
Yeah, just a little legwork.
Nothing you're not used to.
How much longer are
we gonna sit here...?
I'm getting kinda bored.
I thought this was important.
Now, about the offer...
Yeah? What about it?
Is it for a permanent position?
Are you gonna take it?
I guess I need to figure out
a few things before I decide.
I don't know yet.
I see.
I apologize for the delay.
I knew you'd be here...
Did you find it?
It wasn't easy, but here it is.
It was published four years ago.
Will this do?
Keep in touch, I'll be around.
Definitely.
I'm outta here.
Ayu, wait! Hold on!
What is it now?
I owe you for this.
No you don't.
Just take it. It's yours.
I just want the
normal Takayuki back
at work tomorrow...
Can you do that?
Thanks!
Yeah, whatever.
I heard that you
came by last night.
I'm really glad that you did...
I was worried that you might
have stopped coming to see her.
Oh, I'd never stop that.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just caught a little cold.
Hey, what's that?
It's a book for Haruka.
Is that Mayal's Gift...?
The one she's been looking for.
The very one.
I got my hands on a rare copy.
She'll be thrilled.
That's just what I'm hoping for.
Thank you, Takayuki.
Huh? What?
Well, I'll see ya
here next time, I guess.
Take care.
You too.
Well, look who's here.
Oh, hello.
You working by yourself tonight?
Yeah, Hotaru's
taking the night off...
so I guess I'm
flying solo tonight.
I see...
This is... This is
how it should be.
I think... you've had
a little too much.
Come on...
I know my limits, Shinji.
We can never go back.
The old days... they were fun.
But they're all gone now...
The good times...
They're all gone. It's over.
It's not over yet...
We can still have fun now.
I love him... I really do.
Even if he still wants
to be with Haruka...
I can't let go of him.
I've never known how to.
I love him so much.
♪ That guy
Takayuki is dumb. ♪
♪ And no one likes,
him at all! ♪
♪ No, no they don't ♪
♪ 'cause he struts around
all over the place! ♪
♪ And he thinks that
he knows everything, ♪
♪ but he doesn't 'cause he's
just an assistant manager ♪
♪ at a crappy restaurant. ♪
♪ I should have his job! ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm
smarter than him! ♪
I hate him!!