I'm starting to get anxious
being stuck in this
bed all the time.
Is something wrong...? You okay?
It's gonna be alright.
Hello?
Hi, Mistuki. You busy right now?
I'm on my lunch break.
What do you need?
Uh, nothing.
Just wanted to say I was
sorry for being late yesterday.
Oh... Okay.
Dinner was great.
Thanks for cooking it up.
So, is that it?
What?
Is that all you
were calling for?
Uh... yeah... sorry...
Are you--I mean, is this
a bad time for you?
No. It's as good a
time as any, I suppose.
Do you want to go out later?
I can't.
There's this company thing.
I have to be there.
Okay. Just don't drink too much.
You know how sake can disagree
with your stomach
if you haven't eaten.
I'll be fine.
I'll let you go then...
Sorry to bother you
in the middle of the day.
No... I'm glad you called...
Have fun at work.
Not possible, but thanks.
Get back to lunch.
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
I feel a sense of
responsibility with Haruka,
but that's all.
You are the one
that I love, Mitsuki.
Hey... Ya think
he's having an affair?
Why else would he sneak off...?
We've gotta teach
this guy a lesson.
As women we should
always stand together...
Cheat on one of us and
the others will find you
and stomp you into the ground!
Whoa... That's great.
We'll show the
women of this town
what he really is...
There's no way he'll ever
find a date here again!
That is one heck of
a plan, young ladies.
Hi, boss.
But... Your time
would be better served
doing the job
you were hired for.
Well, Mayu!
What is it, Ayu?
We've got a ton
of work... Let's go!
Right!
Boss... What's up with them?
Just another plan
to take you down.
Sorry about that.
Long conversation...
I didn't know when you'd
be finished, so I started.
I would have, too.
Sounds to me like there's
trouble brewing in paradise.
Covering up your
feelings might've
worked in school,
but not in the real world.
Out here, if you
have a bad time,
people can see right through it.
Stop taking
everything so seriously.
Loosen up and things around
you will loosen up, too.
What do you know about me?
You think you've got
me all figured out,
but you have no idea
what I'm dealing with.
I'm sorry...
That was so rude of me.
I was wondering
when that human side
of you was going to come out.
What do you say we
enjoy ourselves tonight?
Hi, Takayuki!
How you doing, Hotaru?
Doing great, thank you...
But you're a little late.
Visiting hours already ended.
We were short staffed,
so I had to work overtime
at the restaurant.
Have you seen Akane?
Yeah. She left here
just a little while ago.
Oh, that's too bad.
Evening, boyfriend.
Did you do something
to Haruka yesterday?
He's not that
kind of guy, Fumie.
Oh, calm down.
I didn't mean that...
Did you two make some
kind of wish or something?
Uh, yeah...
How... sweet...
He's such a romantic.
It's just something we said...
but Haruka's always
liked to call it a wish.
What brought that up?
A wish...
You mean wishing on a star...?
Like, the poem?
Kinda, but it
wasn't the same words.
I think she made it up.
She always had me
repeat the words she said.
Why are you asking?
Did she say something?
She danced around the
subject when I asked her...
but no one looks that
excited about something
if they aren't.
She's remembered something.
Yep... It's coming back...
She's been remembering
a buncha stuff...
And she's been holding on
to the memories for a while.
Hotaru, that's not
your place to say.
You're just a nurse.
But he's her boyfriend...
So, he should know.
That's for the doctor to say.
You started it... Remember.
But, at any rate--
She's remembering things.
And that's what matters...
I won't tell anyone.
Thanks... We need our jobs.
She's remembering
because of you.
Oh... No.
You're late, Takayuki.
Hi, Doctor.
Long day slinging coffee?
Yeah.
I know it's after hours,
but can I see her?
Sure... Go on...
She's been waiting
for you all day.
Cool... Thanks.
Hey!
Where have you been?
Working late.
Sorry. How are you doing?
Oh... Great...
Especially now that you're here.
I'm happy.
It's gonna be alright.
Is something wrong?
I don't have food
on my face again do I?
Oh, no... I just...
I pulled an all-nighter last
night...
I guess I'm still
kinda dazed-out from it.
I bet...
You shouldn't do that...
Getting no sleep
will wear you out.
Nah... Besides, if I don't put
in the hours studying...
I'll fail.
There's tons of
time until the exams.
You don't have
to break your back.
You're right.
I'll be more
careful with myself.
You promise?
Yeah. Of course I do.
Are you serious?
Thanks for that.
Are you bored?
No, I'm having a great time.
So this is what
you always look like
when you're having fun?
I'm sorry.
Even your apologies sound bored.
Forget about that
boyfriend for a while.
Alright, let's get
this evening rolling!
Who's our first victim tonight?
Here...! I've had
just enough to drink...!
And Mitsuki's singing with me!
Huh?!
Chill out, will ya...?
Time to cut loose.
But I'm a terrible singer,
you have no idea!
Oh, I seriously doubt that...
So... Who wants to hear some
old fashioned rock and roll?
You're gonna love this.
These people are so drunk,
they wouldn't even know
if you sang like a dying cat.
Well?
Yeah.
Come on, fellas!
Let's rock this joint.
This is nice.
Once more...?
You can't get
enough of that wish.
Sorry. I didn't know
it was becoming annoying.
I didn't mean it like that.
Then...
Let's do it again.
Sure.
Come on legs...
I think you had a few
too many of those big beers.
Yep! And I coulda
had a few more.
You finally got
that mood off the ground.
Well... I have you
to thank for it--
Oh, watch it!
Here.
I'm okay.
Do I need to call a cab?
No...! It's alright!
No... I'll be fine.
Everything's gonna be alright.
Even if these hands
ever pull apart...
The connection between
us will never be betrayed.
Takayuki...
Sis... I forgot my bookbag--
Oh... Okay...
Akane, it's... It's not...
Akane!
Akane! Hold up!
You're overreacting!
What are you doing?
Me?!
What am I doing?
You don't have
any feelings for her!
You don't... know that.
I don't?
You shouldn't even
be here, Takayuki!
You wouldn't even be here
if I hadn't called you!
You stopped seeing her.
You turned your back
on a helpless person
and gave your
heart to someone else.
You don't love my sister.
You love her.
So, quit playing
with Haruka's emotions.
Just leave her alone.
For the sake of all of us.
You're wrong.
You're wrong about me.
You don't know me.
You're wrong.
I didn't expect to
see you... here. Mitsuki?
Welcome home, Takayuki!
You're smashed...
What were you drinking?
I'm not drunk.
What're you looking at?
Oh... Just a few things...
With all the drama around here,
we had to put it
off for a while...
I thought, why not get this
apartment train rolling again.
You know, since
Haruka's getting better,
I thought we should...
I found a nice place.
It's a tad on
the expensive side.
But I think we can afford it.
We split the rent,
go out a few less times
a month and we're good.
It's near the station,
which is perfect.
And it's a... you know...
it's a... corner unit!
It's got a killer view.
It'll go fast, so we
need to head out there
this weekend and
take a look... 'Kay?
I can call the
rental agent tomorrow
and set up a time.
So what day's gonna
work out better for you?
Me...?
I think Saturday
would work out best,
because then the--Whatcha
got there...?
Hey, thanks, so what's
your weekend looking like?
Wait-wait!
Not Saturday. I gotta client.
That's right.
I guess Sunday would
be a better day then...
Whaddaya say to that?
Is Sunday gonna work
out okay for you?
Slow down.
Let's wait on it.
This moving in thing--It's
not the kind of thing
we need to be rushing into...
We can do it once
Haruka's been released
from the hospital.
Wait... This doesn't
make any sense...
You're the one who said we
should find a place together...
You're the one who
took me out of here
to find a place we both wanted.
I know... But Haruka--
What does she have
to do with any of this?!
What difference does it make
if that sad little girl
is better or dead?!!
This is our business!
She has nothing to do with us!
Why are you acting
like a crazy person?
Because that's how I feel!
Thanks to you!
You're drunk...
I never said we
couldn't move in together.
Have you even told her?
I bet she has no idea...
When do you plan on
breaking the news...?
Or would you rather keep the
two of us a secret forever?
What...?
You... You're losing it.
Am I? Or am I dead right?
Tell me!
I don't need to take this!
Next time you wanna get bombed
and yell at someone,
pick another apartment.
Psycho...
Wait!
What are you doing...?
You could hit
somebody with those!
I'm drunk...
So what about it...?
I need something to turn
to since I don't have you...
Everything has
turned so miserable.
I can barely lift
my head in the mornings.
What's happening to you...?
What's brought all this on?
You still love her.
You love Haruka
more than you love me.
That's not true.
Of course it is...
I'm not blind to
how you look at her.
You're wrong...
I'm not in love with her.
I swear it...
Remember I told you...
It's gonna be alright?
You don't believe that, do you?
Of course I do!
No!
You don't know how you feel...!
And you don't
treat someone you love
the way you've treated me!
Mitsuki...! Don't run off!
Mitsuki!
Thanks for coming in.
You kids were so
well behaved today...
What's wrong with him?
He seems more
depressed than usual.
I would say that his
steamy love affair went sour
and now he's emotionally
bankrupt inside.
Oh... That would
make a lot of sense.
The hopeless romantic
crashed and burned.
Ah... Takayuki,
just who I wanted.
Hi, boss. What can I do for you?
I'd like to introduce you.
This is Mr. Ito, the director
of Human Resources
from corporate.
It's a pleasure to meet you...
This is my card.
Nice to meet you.
I was just telling Mr. Ito
what an excellent
floor manager you are.
Thanks.
Takayuki, you're not currently
enrolled in college are you?
No... Why?
Is there any particular
reason you're not?
Well, I just didn't, um--
Oh, how rude of me...
I don't even know you
and I say that...
I got ahead of myself...
I'm running late so
I have to go now...
But I'll be back later in
the week to check on things.
Good to see you, Mr. Ito.
Nice to meet you, Takayuki.
You, too.
He's a busy man.
You were lucky to talk to him.
Why would the director
of Human Resources come here?
Still can't figure
it out, huh, genius?
There's a certain person
working in the restaurant
whose mind is always
swimming in thoughts
of lust, greed,
and slacking off.
Word of this idiot made its way
up to the head office...
and they sent their
man to investigate,
'cause if they let
this guy stay on...
The Sky Temple's
name will be soiled.
Who would do
something like that, Ayu?
Who do you think?
If they don't can him soon,
his behavior will bring
down the restaurant.
No... They can't shut us down!
I need this job!
Oops.
Oh... I'm so disappointed
in you, Takayuki.
I would never let that happen.
Here... Let me show
you the real problem.
Here come the
false accusations--
If anyone's
hurting our reputation,
it's gonna be
little miss pig-tails.
Say that to my face, jerk!
You do have a nasty attitude.
No! He makes me like this!
But, Ayu, I thought
you were on our side!
Have you lost your mind?!
I dunno...
I have heard you out there...
'How long does it take you
to pick out a dessert...?!
Tell me you want the cake,
like you always do,
you fat tub-a-lard!'...
That's behavior I would have to
question in this line of work.
You... You're so lying...
I've never spoken
such rude things.
I'm telling the truth...
Aren't I, Mayu?
Yep...!
She talks like that
to all the customers.
I do not!!
I think we got a witness, boss.
I guess I'll contact corporate.
'Kay... You can stop...
We're done now.
Now... That's... it!!!
You're still on the clock!
You go after him now and
you'll get fired for sure!
Let go of me...
I know what I'm doing.
I'm gonna get back to work.
I'll be on the
floor if you need me.
Sure... I'm gonna
watch this thing play out.
Right.
Come here...! Coward!
You think you can
just get away with that?!
You're busted...
Don't make it worse!
I hate you so much...
I hope you step in cat crap!
Hi, this is Mitsuki.
I'm not anywhere near my phone
because I'm a busy girl
and that's just how we are.
If you want to, leave
a message after the beep,
and I'll get back to you
if I want to. Bye.
Oh. I didn't realize
that she'd be asleep.
Yeah... She crashed early.
They ran a whole slew
of tests on her today...
I think it just wore her out.
I'd be tired, too.
Sorry you came all the
way out here for nothing.
It's still good to see you.
Thanks... I'll be
back tomorrow afternoon.
Sure... And we'll still be here.
Takayuki, did you hear?
What?
About what happened
to Haruka's sister.
Something happened to Akane?
Yeah, she won another
huge swimming meet!
Oh... Right.
She's doing really
well this season...
When her mom was
here earlier today,
she couldn't stop going
on about how well it went.
Yeah... That sounds like her.
She's just amazing...
I hear she's practically a
shoe-in for the Olympic team...
And one day, I'm gonna
swim as well as her.
How's that gonna happen
if you're in the
nursing program?
I can do it... Trust me...
It's just gonna
take really hard work.
That's great...
She's living the dream.
I heard about the swim meet.
You've been working pretty hard.
Oh, well...
Welcome home.
Thanks.
I'm sorry about yesterday...
how I acted.
But I've made a decision.
I wanna live here
with you, Takayuki.
Is that alright?
Hello?
I think my new
boyfriend might ditch me
and go back to
his old girlfriend
and I just don't know what
to do about the whole thing.
I'm losing my mind.
Who cares?
What is it?
You hung up on me
without giving me any advice.
What's the deal?
You're an idiot!
I'm so sick of this!
Would you two get out
of the conference room
and get back to work?
Who cares you idiot!