Thanks again for
bringing the flowers.
It's my pleasure.
Thank you.
I'm so happy that
you're feeling alright...
You look really great.
You can make up
for the lost time.
Don't worry.
Takayuki?
What is it, Haruka?
I'm so happy right now.
Huh?
Just being able to
spend time with you...
and seeing your smiling face...
It helps me through the day.
But...
Don't force yourself.
I mean...
Three years is a long time.
I know that life
moved on without me...
I guess I should...
start getting used to that.
Haruka.
I don't think I can handle
taking in everything at once.
Like, my brain will
explode if I try.
I want you to bring me
up to date slowly on
what I've missed
while I've been asleep.
But...
There is something...
I'd like to know now.
It's the one question
that means the most.
What is it?
Takayuki...?
Are you seeing anyone right now?
No matter what your answer is...
I can handle it.
Is there anyone else...?
Please tell me.
There's no one else.
I'm single...
I'm not seeing anyone.
Honestly?
I have no reason
to lie to you, Haruka.
I see... That's good to hear.
Hey.
So, is it true?
I said I wasn't lying.
You and Mitsuki really broke up?
Akane?
Is there something wrong?
Huh?, No, I'm fine...
I just... I completely forgot
to tell Takayuki something.
Oh, okay.
Hey, Akane.
Yeah?
I wonder how Mitsuki's doing.
Oh.
Do you think she's busy tonight?
It'd be great
if she could visit.
Okay.
Let's make sure the
vouchers for Ginseng Mart
and 3G are taken care
of by the end of the day.
We also need to start
on travel arrangements.
Can you stay late today?
Sure... I'm ready to go.
You can go home if you want.
Huh? But...
I'll cover tonight...
But don't worry, you'll have
plenty to do in the morning.
Okay, thanks.
It's been a long time.
Mistuki...
Now all that's
left to do is for you
to sign on the dotted line.
Right.
Great... Barring
any sudden changes...
your first day on the job
will be two weeks from today...
I'll be in touch with you soon
about the necessary paperwork.
Thank you for the opportunity.
I'm very happy for you, son.
Thanks.
Did I hear that right...?
Takayuki's leaving
us for another job?
Wait, where're you going?
Back to work, Mayu.
Huh?
Why am I upset about this?
I should be thrilled...
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
That scum sucker!
What was that?
Ah... I wouldn't
worry about her...
I think she just
has a screw loose.
Oh.
You look like a grown up now.
You think so, huh?
Well, yeah...
And I love your hair.
Oh... thanks.
It is pretty different.
I heard you've got a cool job...
You like it?
Yeah, but the
hours can be tough.
I heard something else.
Did you really...
quit swimming...
your senior year?
Oh.
Yeah... I did.
But, why?
Well, I guess
I just reached my limit...
And I...
Your limit?
I'm sorry.
I'll tell you the
real reason why I quit.
Huh?
Haruka... Takayuki...
And I... started dating.
I'm so sorry.
You're lying.
Please, Mitsuki...
Tell me it's a lie.
Did you know of this?
Why?
Why would you do that...?
I have to know.
I'm sorry...
It's just that after
you got in that accident
a lot of things
kind of happened.
It's over, though.
We're broken up now.
This whole thing is my fault.
Please understand...
It's not like...
I was ever in
love with Takayuki.
It wasn't like that.
How should I put this...?
Anyone would have done
it in my situation.
You have no idea
how hard it was.
But, don't get me wrong,
I wasn't trying to hurt you...
I was weak and
I let that control me.
Takayuki was there,
so I went with it.
But don't worry...
I really don't have any
feelings at all for Takayuki.
Haruka. Please, forgive me.
Get out.
I said get out of my room!
I can't blame Mitsuki
for what happened.
It's me...
If I had never got
into that accident,
I could have been
there at his side
when he really needed me.
It's okay.
It's not fair!
It's not.
Wasn't the view from
that apartment great?
I just can't compete
with Haruka any longer.
Sorry I'm late.
It's about time you showed!
Come on, let's go.
Well look who it is.
Hey.
What's wrong?
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
Nothing.
Say, you got a minute to spare?
Well... I don't have to
be at work for another hour.
Oh really.
You wanna grab a drink?
Sure.
I've been running
around all morning
without any caffeine ...
I can't even think straight.
You're not even
listening to me are you?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to drag
you here against your will.
Oh no... I don't mind.
You were just standing there...
Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine,
I was just daydreaming.
Cool... You looked
like a zombie though...
So, work at the hospital
is way busy now.
But that should
come as no surprise
since Hotaru's not there.
Huh?, She's still on vacation?
I thought she'd be back by now.
That's right, no one told you...
Hotaru quit her job at
the hospital and moved away.
Since her last day
I haven't even heard from her.
I'm sorry.
Yeah...
It really sucks because
I guess she contracted
some weird illness that
keeps her bed ridden...
She's living with her parents
now until she gets better.
Oh no. Is she gonna be alright?
Yeah, I think she's
gonna be fine...
She may be physically
weak right now,
but she's strong willed,
which goes a long way...
If you think about it,
she and Haruka
are kind of in the
same boat right now.
You know the feeling
where you spend
so much time with someone
that you take it for granted?
But once that person's gone
you feel a huge
hole in your heart?
Well, that's how
I feel every time
I step inside that hospital.
But I guess it
won't do me any good
if I try to run
away from it, huh?
Wait... I'm not the
one that's running away
from my problems...
You know...?
Gee, I wonder who
I'm referring to.
Well, it was bound
to happen sometime.
Morning everyone.
Good morning...
How you doing, Takayuki?
Is there something wrong?
No... I'm fine...
It's just gonna be
lonely here without you.
Oh.
Just a few days left
'til your new job...
We're gonna miss
all your hard work.
Thank you, sir.
Siberia sure is cold.
What are you talking about?
Duh...! We're talking
about your demotion!
Demotion?
You've been hired by the
suits from corporate, right?
The only place an
executive would consider
sending you is a worthless post
at the ass end of the earth.
I'm sure they've
put you in charge
of herding the
penguins or something.
Shepherd boy!
You know, I'd rather do that
than have to listen to
you for one more second...
Besides there are no penguins
in Siberia, you dumbass.
Let go! Let go! Let go! Let go!
No penguins?
What happened to them?
Penguins are from the
southern hemisphere...
Whoever told you that
they're found in the...
This is pointless.
There are too
penguins up there...!
Haven't you ever heard of a zoo?
You'll find plenty
of them there, stupid.
Oh crap! Mayu!
We've got eight tables waiting!
Eight tables?!
Those two are nuts.
I saw you laughing and
tickling that girl back there,
so don't try to act
like you're innocent!
I'm not the one that's
running away from my problems.
Neither am I... No way.
I'm going to
tell her everything.
No more deception.
She's not in there.
You just missed her.
So she's already started rehab?
Yes.
A friend of hers
visited the other day,
and she's really turned
it around since then.
A friend, huh?
She's a tough girl.
I haven't seen determination
like that in years.
Huh?
What's he doing here?
How embarrassing...
I wish you wouldn't
have seen me like that...
Pretend you didn't.
Yeah, sure... I understand...
but you know
something, Haruka...?
For someone who's been bedridden
for so long your
progress is amazing.
Thank you ...
All I'm doing is trying my best.
And it shows...
Really... just promise me that
you won't over exert yourself.
I can't do that.
In my entire life...
I haven't done much of
anything to be proud of...
Now it's either a hundred
and ten percent or nothing.
You've done a lot.
Hey, Sis...
I think it's fine if
you wanna push yourself...
just promise not to do
anything that'll make me
have to work harder, okay?
Okay... I'll remember that.
Great.
Should we head back?
Wait, let me help you with that.
I'll do it.
Don't worry. I can manage it.
But thank you.
See ya later.
Hey, Akane.
Hey, are you waiting
here to see Haruka?
Uh, no. I was just sitting here.
Really? You must be bored.
Mitsuki came by the
hospital about a week ago.
Who?
Your ex-girlfriend.
She was here?
She came by and...
talked with Haruka.
Oh... So that's why...
she started rehab.
It makes sense... I had no idea.
Haruka's stronger than
I ever imagined her to be.
The girl I knew
before the accident was
so shy and fragile.
The type of girl
that'd be scared of a bee
and could never harm a fly.
I always used to
think that she was
in a constant
state of daydreaming,
totally disconnected
from reality.
But watching her try to
learn how to walk again,
drenched in sweat.
That just blew me away.
Ever since she woke up
she's been an
entirely different person.
Is that what you really think?
Huh?
Move! I said move!
Why?! They're my legs dammit!
Why won't they move?!
How am I supposed
to live my life
without being able to walk?!
How can I ask him
to be by my side...
when I'm so helpless...?!
I lost three whole years...
I hate this! It's not fair!
Why did this have
to happen to me...?
What did I do
to deserve this...?
I just want my life back!
It still really hurts me...
how nice you always are.
You're like a disease.
Everyone you surround
yourself with suffers.
I trust you can take
care of yourself now, right?
I'm not the one that's
running away from my problems.
I'm... I'm so stupid.
Dammit... Dammit!
Dammit!!!
Keep it up, Haruka!
You're almost to the end.
Hey.
Hi, Takayuki.
Why are you here...?
Don't you have work?
I need to talk to
you about something...
Is that okay?
Dumped, all alone after trying
to handle two women.
I'm free!
He prattled along blindly.
And ended up in
the hospital himself.
Don't stop! Keep going!
I can't keep going, dummy.
That was the end.
And it's the
most fabulous ending
for a stupid
blockhead jerk like him!
Quit yapping that trap of yours!
I'm sick of hearing it!
Just breathe!
Mayu! Help me!
Good job! Come on,
teach that girl a lesson!
Go, Takayuki! I can do it!
Don't miss the final episode!