This isn't even close
to what I ordered!
Yeah.
I ordered the
strawberry parfait...
Not the French onion soup.
Don't you understand that?
Strawberry parfait, genius...
Take this and go get me
what I ordered, 'kay?
Uh, huh.
What are you, chicky?
Some kinda flippin' retard?
Whatever.
Hello? This is
your fault, twerp!
Just apologize and fix it...
Now, scurry along.
Mm-hm.
You suck!
Would you just get me
the food I ordered?!
Right.
I said I wanted my food!
Ok.
Oh... this isn't good...
What'll we do?
Same as usual.
Where are you going?!
I'm gonna get
the problem solver.
Okay, but make it fast,
before Ayu gets...
Welcome to Sky Temple.
Table for one this evening?
Are you just gonna stand
there like a zombie...
or are you gonna be a good skirt
and get me my food?
Sure.
Little runt... I'm gonna--
I'm anything but little.
Shut up!
Dude... Now that's funny.
I ordered a
strawberry parfait...
and, I'm gonna get
a strawberry parfait.
Would you like
some French fries--
You know, you've got one
heck of a set on ya, Mister!
Just because you're unhappy
with the person you've
become doesn't mean
you can take it out on me!
You're nuts!
Shut up!
You think you can walk
in here and pick a fight...
guess what...
You picked the wrong girl
at the wrong restaurant
on the wrong day,
ya slimy bottom-feeder...!
Now, bring it on!!
What kinda place are
you guys running here...?
You're supposed to
serve the customers,
not pick fights with them!
Yeah...?
Well, I got a few other ideas of
what we should do
with the customers--
Ayu... What've
I told you about this?
Let go of me, ya sewer rat!
I apologize for
her behavior, sirs...
I'll have the parfait
brought out immediately.
Don't do that! They suck!
It's over, Ayu.
Let it go...
Again, I'm sorry for this.
You should have
her cleaning toilets,
not working the floor!
Yeah... Keep talking!
I'll find you in
the parking lot!
Hey! Get off me.
Stop fighting
and get back there!
I can't seem to figure out
what your deal is...
Who mixes up strawberry parfait
with French onion soup
and then gets ticked off
at the customer for it?
Shut up!
You idiot.
I am not...! You're the idiot!
You think so?
Takayuki, great work out there.
Oh... Thank you, sir.
The customer is always right
and you always
seem to know that.
You were wonderful out there.
I wish I could handle
things as well as you do.
Well, it's not the customers
who are hard to handle.
It's Ayu.
I am not hard to handle!!
As you can tell by the fact
that you pulled my cheeks
until they're beet red!
I better get back on the floor.
Sounds good.
Are you even listening to me?
Wait!
Stop making a
scene out here, Ayu.
I'm not making a scene!
And I sure as hell ain't
finished with you...!
It's time we went to town!
What?
That guy was right...
You should be
cleaning the toilets.
And you... you can go...
Step in cat crap!
Do you want this job...?
'Cause I don't think
you have any idea
how nice a restaurant this is.
I know more than you think I do!
You're an idiot...
And idiots wash the dishes...
I don't wanna see you out here.
Not the dishes!
I'm sorry everybody.
Please enjoy your meals.
Mitsuki...
So...
You got women waving at you.
So what?
Do you have any
idea who she is...
'cause she's pretty.
She is a hot number...
Is that your girlfriend
or just an admirer?
She's no one.
No... You're lying...
I can so tell.
That's enough...
You're supposed
to be washing dishes.
You don't have to push!
Cut it out!
I just wanted to know
if that's the girlfriend
we've heard about!
Get off!
What's up? You're so quiet.
You seem distracted.
Yeah.
Come on. What's bothering you?
It's just, this
is the first time
I've ever seen you at work.
Do you actually
enjoy working there?
Not really. But it's a job.
Oh, well it looked fun.
You looked happy.
Come on in. How many?
There'll be three.
Our friend will be meeting us.
Yo...! Takayuki...! Mitsuki...!
I got us a table!
I guess he's already here.
Sorry, I started without you.
That's cool.
Man, it feels like forever
since the three of us hung out.
I thought you were
gonna be running late?
What happened?
Did your plans fall through?
Yeah, my date cancelled
on me at the last minute,
so I thought I'd head
on over and start eating.
What was her excuse?
Is she your girlfriend?
She said that the deadline
for her article
got changed again
so she was gonna have
to pull an all-nighter.
And is she my girlfriend...? No.
Cheers!
Excuse me...
This will only take
a second. Hello?
I'm not surprised...
So they'll have eight more, huh?
Then go ahead and
make the reservation
for twenty, that'll give us
the whole back room...
Right.
Great, thanks.
I'll see ya tomorrow.
Sorry about that.
Sounds like you're
throwing a party.
Some retirement for
an old-timer I work with.
Can you believe they
put me in charge of it?
Oh, man, what
were they thinking?
Come on, dude;
I'm different these days...
I'm good at my job
and the people
who work for me
really respect me.
I guess things are really
looking up for you.
Yeah and what about you...
Mr. Part-Timer?
Those waitresses
working under you are hot.
I've seen 'em.
Bet you've been with
every one of 'em, haven't you?
What... n-no... I...
You want some of that.
Especially the blonde...
There's a lady at the table.
So, uh, Mitsuki...
How's your work...?
Have you moved up in the world,
unlike Takayuki here?
Uh, no...
It's a small company so there's
really no ladder to climb.
I'm kinda stuck...
They're so shorthanded,
and they won't hire
any new people,
so they moved me to sales.
Lots of overtime, though.
That's the one upside, yeah...
But if I hadn't been
out on sales calls all
afternoon they would have
kept me there all night.
So, since I was out anyway...
I just kinda figured
I wouldn't go back tonight.
Smart move.
So both of you are still single
and work so much that
you can't be bothered
with taking the
time to date someone.
That's right.
I'll call you guys next week.
Good seeing you, man!
Take care!
Time sure flies, doesn't it...?
I know it's kinda late...
but we can still do
something if you want.
You know...
The only thing I wanna do
tonight is stay in your arms...
Is that okay?
I want you.
Me, too.
But, I...
Takayuki...
Hey...
You know that
world aquarium downtown?
Yeah.
They have sea otters ...
You wanna go see
'em this weekend...
They're supposed to
be really beautiful.
Sea otters?
Yeah. What about Sunday?
I can't Sunday.
I've got a double shift at work.
Oh, I understand.
How 'bout next weekend?
Wha--what are you doing?
So... let's move in together?
We could be like
this all the time
without having to plan so much.
Yeah...
We could get a cat...
And we could move into a
place twice this size...
Sound nice?
Oh, come on...
We can't afford
anything like that.
Not even with our
salaries combined.
Yeah.
I guess you're right...
I don't know what
I was thinking, just then.
Go, Mitsuki! You can do it!
Hurry...! You're winning!
Finishing first, lane
three, Mitsuki Hayase!
It's nice out there today.
Okay, I'm leaving for work.
Hey, you know you
should try to spend
some time outdoors, even
if it is just on the balcony.
Uh-huh. Have a good one.
I'll do my best.
Mitsuki?
Uh-huh?
Do you really want
to live together?
Well, you said it last night.
And I was just thinking,
maybe we should.
You could move in.
You mean live here...?
In your place?
Yeah, right...
Isn't that what you wanted?
Well...
I dunno... We can
talk about this later.
I'm running late.
This place hasn't changed
since before the accident...
I can't live here.
Downtown train is
arriving at Platform Two.
Please stand clear
until the train has come
to a complete stop.
Mitsuki, is everything lined up
for today's sales meetings?
Yes, ma'am.
There're more samples
there than you're used to,
but I bet you can handle it...
You're still young.
Of course.
Looks like you had a fun time
with your boyfriend last night.
You're wearing the same
clothes from yesterday...
It's kinda tacky.
You need to be more mindful
about your appearance...
A professional look
is important in sales.
It won't happen again...
I'm sorry.
Well...
The only reason
I noticed is because
I used to do the same thing.
I can't believe you
got a driver's license!
Yup. It's sweet.
I'm so jealous of you...
This is the coolest ever.
It took me three years to
get my hands on this card.
You for real...?
It only took you three years
to get your license?
I was the fastest learner
in my whole class.
You mind telling me
what you two are doing
on the floor instead of working?
We're just having
a little chat...
Now feast your eyes on this!
What...?! Are you stupid?
What are you talking about?
This is my driver's license...
Hot off the presses.
I thought you said
you hadn't driven
anything since you got your
learner's permit last year.
So what...?
That doesn't change a thing...
I still got my license
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
Why would I want to...?
Anyway, there's
nothing to brag about
if you're not going to use it.
Would you go away?!
Mayu, listen,
if someone like her can get
one of those, then you should
be able to with no problems.
Wow... You really think so?
Stop making fun of me,
you sewer rat!
I wasn't making fun of you.
He's telling the truth.
You're not my friend...
I hadn't ever planned on getting
my driver's license anyway.
So it's no big deal.
Really...? How come?
Because I'm scared...
I'd hate to be in an accident.
Yes... accidents are scary...
They can ruin
your life forever...
and that's precisely why
I don't drive anywhere...
Is that a good enough
reason for you, rat?!
What...? Oh, did
you say something?
I wasn't listening.
Cut it out, guys...
We got tables out there
full of hungry people.
Sure... I'm going.
I'm not done with
you yet, you filthy pig!!
Calm down, Ayu.
It's a pleasure
doing business with you.
Okay. We only have two more
to do so let's hurry...
After that let's grab
some lunch. I'm hungry
Okay.
I tell you, I didn't think
that guy would ever shut up.
I wish our clients would
consider our time for a change.
But that would require
thoughtful clients,
which I don't know if we have.
Are they heavy?
Oh, no... I guess
I'm just not used
to all this walking around.
Yeah.
You'll get used to it;
we all do.
Maybe I should
start working out.
So you have a big date tonight?
Uh... No, not really.
Don't like your
job much, do you?
What?
It's not what you had planned.
Well, it's not what
I had planned either,
but you roll with the punches.
So how are things going
with your boyfriend?
Oh... not bad...
Sorry...!
Just making conversation.
Oh... Things are moving along...
Just kinda slowly.
Yay, Mitsuki! You can do it!
What's wrong?
What?
You... zoned out...
Is something wrong?
Oh, I'm sorry...
I got distracted.
Ouch.
Mitsuki...!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Oh, no. I'm so clumsy.
Takayuki?
I'm sorry to bother you,
but can we meet later?
I'll be at the
station around seven.
Hey, you.
You alright?
You haven't touched
your noodles...
Something wrong?
Yes.
Let's be honest with
each other. About us.
Ok, I'm just gonna come
right out and tell you...
I can't do this...
It's like we're standing still.
And I love you, Takayuki.
I can't help it.
I really love you.
But I need to know...
Do you love me, too?
Of course, I love you.
You do?
More than you know.
Oh, Takayuki...
I'm so happy you said that.
So you were serious about
the whole moving in thing?
Yeah...
If that's what you want
then I'm all for it...
It'll be fun.
This is important,
so we need to take our time.
I don't want to just get
into the first place we find.
I want it to be our place.
Our decision. Together.
I want that, too.
You ready?
You're so warm...
You know what...
I wanna stay like this with
you for as long as we can.
Then I'll be right next
to you the whole time.
Yeah... That's what I want.
Are you gonna stay over tonight?
Can't.
My boss noticed I wore the
same clothes as yesterday.
So nothing for you tonight.
You're just gonna have
to make do on your own.
Arm-in-arm will have
to do for us this evening.
Okay.
This year's swim team.
From our old school... Neat.
Thanks so much for the burger!
Yeah, thanks a lot...
Captain Suzumiya.
Don't worry about it, guys...
And enough with this
'captain' stuff.
Call me Akane.
Besides, hanging out
with you guys is a blast.
But you're gonna
have to train harder
if you want me
to keep this up...
Here, I'll light
a fire under you.
Tomorrow the slowest
lap time buys me dinner!
But that'll be me.
Maybe not, you know...
Tomorrow is a new day.
It's getting late.
We should call it a night...
You three be safe
going home, ok.
We will! Thank you, Akane.
Have a good night!
Good, I still have time.
Akane...
Akane... Seems like ages.
I haven't seen you
in a while, Takayuki.
I gotta get over
to the hospital...
Hopefully I can make it there
before visiting hours end
for the day... Well, see ya.
It's finally time for us, Mayu!
That's right, Ayu.
Ayu, are you all right?
Don't die on stage!
Oh, this is nothing!
Besides if I died, we
wouldn't have much of a show.
Preach the word, sister!
Yeah, yeah!
No!
I'm ok...
Now let's show them
just how wonderful we are.
Right on!
Let's start with...
Wait!