You're right, Haruka.
This is a lie. Every bit of it.
It's been a little
over three years now...
Nobody told you that you've been
in a coma since the
day of the accident.
Everyone is determined
to keep the truth from you.
Everyone has been lying
to you from the beginning.
If you hadn't been at
the train station that day...
everything would
have been fine...
Everyone's hurting--
Sorry, Akane...
This is... this is all my fault
What are you doing?
It keeps falling off of here.
The sucker just won't stay on.
Listen, Mitsuki...
Here, let me help you.
Takayuki.
I'm so sorry...
I was standing right there,
but I just couldn't help.
We heard what happened.
It's not your fault.
Actually, we're the ones
that should be
apologizing to you...
We should never have put this
responsibility on your
shoulders, Takayuki.
No really... I, uh...
Takayuki, do you know
where Akane went?
I think I saw her
leave through that door.
Thank you.
Now where would you go...
I wonder...
Hey, it's Takayuki.
Has Akane shown back up yet?
Ok, then I'll keep looking...
No, no. It's no trouble at all.
Why?
Why did you show up, Shinji?
Why'd you have to
try to play hero?
I...
Why didn't you just ignore me
and keep on going
with your perfect life?
Mitsuki, I just...
I couldn't let you go in
there with some stranger...
I wanted to protect you.
I get that, Shinji.
But I didn't want
this to be with you.
I don't understand...
Why...? Why did
it have to be you?
Why didn't...
Why'd you have to stop me?
Was it that you pitied me?
It isn't like that at all.
Did I seem...
that pathetic to you?
Well maybe I am...
I have nothing left...
was I not supposed
to love him...
Was it really
such a bad thing...?
Was giving up on swimming
for him so terrible?
Was keeping it from
Haruka so bad...?
Am I that terrible
of a person...?
Does everything I do
have to hurt someone?
Will you tell
Takayuki what happened?
I don't think I can face him.
Yes?
Sure, I'll let him know
right away, no prob.
Mayu, who was that?
Oh, it was Takayuki.
He said his cold has
gotten a lot worse,
so he won't be coming
in to work today.
What...?! Sick my ass!
He's just a lazy,
freaking no good loser!
I bet he just wanted
to take a few days
off to play hooky.
There appears to be no
indication of brain damage.
She isn't in a coma but,
it seems that the
psychological shock threw
her brain into a kind
of self-protection mode.
However, this is
a very rare type
of illness and there is no
information on the subject.
So basically my
analysis is guesswork.
All we can do right now is try
to protect her from any
more outside stimulation.
Other than that,
we can all make sure
to be there for her
when she wakes up.
Thank you so much
for your help, Doctor.
Doc, how is Haruka?
Are you all right?
I'm ok... I think
I'm over the worst part.
You need rest...
That's my professional opinion.
I'm sorry for causing
you so much grief.
Go home and rest...
If the situation changes,
we'll let you know first thing.
I promise.
Uh, but I--
No buts.
I know you're
worried about Akane,
but she's a big girl now.
I'm sure she'll be all
right when we find her.
Okay.
Takayuki?
Akane.
I'm sorry if I made you worry.
Yeah, don't sweat it...
I'm just glad you're okay.
How is my sister doing?
She's... in Intensive Care.
Oh.
I just can't believe it!
After three years, she
finally wakes up, and I...
Oh, Takayuki, what if
she never wakes up again?
She'll be ok.
It's all my fault.
Because I... Because I kept...
I kept lying to her.
It's all my fault.
We all lied...
That's what they
told us to do...
It's not your fault
that they said that.
No... I betrayed her, Takayuki!
I said horrible things.
I told her about
you and Mitsuki.
I blamed Mitsuki and
I even blamed my sister.
How is she to blame?
What did she do wrong?
I'm a horrible sister.
No, Akane...
Haruka's in the hospital,
because of me...
I was supposed to meet her
at the station that
day but I was late...
If I'd been on time,
things would be fine now.
Haruka, would never have been
in that horrible accident...
No one would be
hurting right now,
if I had just managed
to get there sooner...
Everything would have
stayed just like it was.
So, you see, it's all my fault.
Not anyone else's...
I never wanted to
hurt anyone. But I did.
Takayuki...
I managed to destroy it all.
I never wanted any of this
and still I betrayed Haruka
and I devastated Mitsuki.
I even managed to hurt you.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Really, I'm ok. Thank you.
Don't worry about your sis...
I had a talk with Doctor
Kozuki about her earlier...
She's gonna recover someday...
I know in my
heart that she will.
Thank you. That's sweet.
It still really hurts me...
how nice you always are.
I did my best to
watch over my sister.
But it wasn't just for her...
It was for you, too.
I thought that if
she ever woke up ...
it would make you happy
and I wanted to see that...
then you'd come back...
You would come to see
her like you always did.
And you would be there
for her when she needed you.
But now...
Now I just feel sorry for her.
Well...
I have to go now...
I owe my parents an explanation
for where I've been...
And I... should try to make up
for all the trouble
that I've caused.
I'm gonna stay by sis's side
and watch over her...
But I'm not gonna do
it for anyone else.
I don't think that's my place.
I'll be the one
who's there for her.
Thank you for everything.
Sorry for taking so long.
Here you go.
Come on, they're not
that bad, are they...?
Yeah, I know they're cheap,
but it's the best I could do.
Besides, you can't
walk on a broken heel.
Wait.
Mitsuki, where are you going?
To work.
But it's already
so late in the day...
you should just take
the rest of it off...
Hey! Wait! Hold up!
Are you all right?
I'm sorry for everything ...
I really am.
I wonder what happened to her.
Stop calling. She's not here.
Hello, Takayuki.
Thank you for coming to
see me on such short notice.
Really, it's no problem at all.
Here's Mitsuki's bag; she
hasn't been in to pick it up.
Thank you.
It sounds like
you've got a cold.
Uh, I'm getting better.
Just been a little
under the weather...
This cold is
getting passed around
like its currency or something.
So, I hear...
Well, when you do see Mitsuki,
would you please tell her
to give me a call
here at the office?
Of course.
Takayuki, it may be
none of my business...
but you really
need to talk to her.
And listen to
what she has to say.
I can't afford for
her personal life
to continue interrupting
my work life.
Yes, ma'am.
The train is arriving
on platform three.
For your safety,
please remain standing
behind the yellow line
until the train
has come to a complete stop.
Well, look who's here.
I'm sorry.
Do you realize that I had
to stay late thanks to you?
I guess I don't mind that much,
considering going home early
is not a priority
for me these days.
Let me help you finish.
Takayuki came by today.
I didn't know when
I was going to see you,
so I gave him your bag.
Oh, thank you.
You should hurry
and get home to him...
If I were you,
I would just forget
about work for today.
Oh, you didn't know
he was sick, did you...?
He looked like he
was about to collapse.
Takayuki...!
What are you doing
just sitting there?
Class is about to
start...! Come on!
Mitsuki...
Takayuki!
This idiot Takayuki
with his problems,
he belongs on trash TV...
Huh...? Who is that?
It's not your
fault they said that.
What was that?!
I...
It's not your fault
they said that--
Ayu!
Oh, no, Mayu!