Takayuki!
We've been through...
a lot, huh?
Haru... ka.
Oh, you're up.
Yeah, hi.
How are you feeling?
You're still a little warm.
Let's take your temperature.
Here... Put it under your arm.
'Kay.
Looks like you've been sweating.
Let me get you some
clean clothes to put on.
You're lucky...
If I hadn't found
you slumped over
your cold might have
turned into pneumonia.
You're so careless sometimes.
Sorry.
Were you just gonna
sleep in the hallway
if I hadn't come home
and moved you to the bed?
You're an adult, Takayuki.
You need to start taking
better care of yourself.
Here.
Go ahead and change into
these clean clothes, okay?
Yeah
Let me guess.
You haven't eaten
anything in days...
How's rice pilaf sound?
Good.
Mitsuki?
What?
I... uh... just forget it.
I'm full.
Already?
Then let me give
you your medicine.
I should call work.
Don't worry about it.
I already took
care of it for you...
Your boss said to take
your time getting better
and get back to work
when you're ready.
Thanks for doing that.
You're welcome. Here.
We haven't done this in a while.
Huh?
You know just hanging
out and talking.
I know.
I've... been lonely.
I should get back to work...
Laundry's waiting.
And you should
get some more sleep.
Hi, Doctor.
I have good news...
Your sister will be out
of intensive care tomorrow.
Will she really?
Yes...
The CAT scan and the
MRI came back negative.
But I'm...
afraid it's not going
to get any easier.
Hi... You're finally awake
Are you starting to feel better?
Yeah.
We'll take your
temperature again later
and see if your fever dropped.
Want something to drink?
Sure.
Hey...
What is it?
I picked up your bag
at the office for you.
Really...? Thank you...
That's so nice of you to do that
even though you
weren't feeling well.
You're such a sweetheart...
You always have been.
Even back in high school...
everyone thought you
were the nicest guy...
so what about you?
You ever think
about the old days?
Yeah.
Me too... It seems
so far away now.
Like it was a different life.
Whenever I think
about those times,
I remember that you
were always there for me
when I needed you.
Oh yeah?
Even though you'd
always complain about it.
When I introduced
you to Haruka...
I thought I was just
helping her out...
you know, because she was so shy
around boys she liked.
I never thought you
two would actually date.
But then...
I never expected to feel
this way about you, either...
Never in a million years.
Then the accident happened.
Haruka fell into a coma...
and before I knew what hit me,
you and I were
dating each other...
I was so happy to be with you.
Yet at the same
time I felt so guilty.
Like I was betraying
Haruka by seeing you.
But no matter what happened,
you were always
there by my side.
And I wanted to be by your side
more than anything
else in the world,
because you were
always so kind...
Not only to me,
but to Haruka as well.
It was all...
Very hard.
I basically gave up everything
so I could devote myself to you.
Then I started to realize ...
if you left me
I would have nothing...
Just, thinking about
that possibility...
It terrified me.
Mitsuki.
I thought if I sabotaged
our relationship...
then maybe the
pain would go away.
And that's why...
last night...
I slept with Shinji...
Whatever you do,
don't be mad at him ...
He's not to blame.
But I... I was so
depressed last night.
I'm sorry I betrayed you.
Aren't you angry at me?
Mitsuki.
I trust you can take care
of yourself now, right?
Don't forget...
Take your antibiotics.
But, Mitsuki wait.
Don't leave!
I have to...
I just can't compete
with Haruka any longer.
Good morning, Akane.
What's up?
How come you're here
so early this morning?
Well...
I have practice later so
this is my only free time.
Just don't work
yourself too hard, okay.
I don't think I do.
Fair enough...
I just don't wanna
see you end up here
for exhaustion or something...
Your sister gave
us quite a scare.
But I'm glad to say
she's pulling through,
because I couldn't stand it
if something bad
happened on my watch.
By the way...
The boyfriend hasn't
been by in a while.
Did something happen?
Oh... I haven't seen him either.
Mayu, get over here!
Your order for
table seven's ready.
Okay!
Damn it...!
How long is that conceited jerk
gonna be on vacation?!
You should spend
some time outdoors,
even if it is just
on the balcony...
Sis...? Are you awake?
Akane?
I'm here, Sis... I'm with you.
Hello?
Takayuki, hi.
This is Sakiyama at Sky Temple.
Oh, hello, sir.
You sound good.
Are you starting to feel better?
Yeah, thanks, much better.
In fact, I think I'm over it.
That's real good to hear.
When do you think you'll
be ready to work again?
We could use you tonight
if you're up to it.
Plus, I was hoping to
discuss something with you.
I can do tonight.
I should be there around five.
Excellent. Thank you.
Hold on someone wants to say hi.
Hey, jerk face!
Where the hell have you been?
Thanks to you,
Mayu and I have been
getting our asses handed to us!
You might wanna think twice
about leaving that little
pleasure cruise of yours,
because I'm gonna make you
pay when I see you again!
Don't think I won't!
Why don't you shut up?
We're sorry.
The number you have dialed has
been disconnected or
is no longer in service.
Hazawa Trading.
It is, but I'm sorry,
Mitsuki will be away from
her desk this afternoon.
That's right...
If you would like to leave a
message I could give it to her.
Goodbye.
Akane... and Dad...? Mom...
Mirror?
What happened to me?
So, how's she doing?
Well, she appears to
be able to understand
that time has passed,
which is good
because that wasn't
the case last time
she came out of her coma.
It's too early to
say for sure, but...
If she keeps moving
at the pace she's on now,
she'll be able to
start rehab very soon.
The necessary
physical adjustments
from having been
asleep for so long
will happen with time.
And as for her mental state,
I'm hoping she'll begin
to accept the reality
of her situation soon...
One more thing...
She has no idea that she woke up
from the coma once before.
Are you serious?
Yes...
Mister Ito from Human
Resources has a position open
and you're first on his list.
He thinks you'd be a perfect
fit for the head office.
Really...?
That's great!
I hope you don't
mind that I went ahead
with this without
asking you first but...
I figured you'd at
least be interested.
Now all you need to
do is say yes or no...
It's a great opportunity
to start a good
career for yourself.
I know, but would you mind
if I took a few days
to think it over?
Sure... let me know
by Friday morning, okay?
Hey look who it is...!
What's up, Takayuki?!
Are you feeling better now?!
It's about time you showed up.
What are you guys doing?
What's it look like?
We're taking our break.
Well that's obvious.
I meant what are you
doing with all this food?
You can't be eating out
in the dining room.
Here. These are for you.
I can see you're hungry.
Go ahead and have some.
What is this?
Man, you're even
dumber than I thought.
It's the receipts for all the
food we've been chowing down on.
And why should
I have to pay for it?
While you were
sitting on your butt
pretending to be sick,
Mayu and I had to
pick up your slack here!
That's why I've
given you this golden
opportunity to
make amends with us.
Let go my face!
Make amends?
Are you freaking kidding me?
You're lucky if I don't
pull your ugly face off first!
You wouldn't dare!
This is no way
to thank the person
who covered your lazy ass!
Don't try to turn
this around on me!
You'll never learn will you?
Oh... We have a customer...
Welcome to Sky Temple.
Dinner for one?
Shinji.
Hey... Can you spare a minute?
So, you've probably talked
to Mistsuki by now, huh.
Yeah.
Then I guess she
told you what happened?
Yeah
I see... Sorry.
You must really
hate my guts right now.
No.
How's Mitsuki doing?
I have no idea... she's gone.
Now what the hell
does that mean?
We broke up.
You broke up...?
And you're okay with that?
It doesn't matter how I feel.
She's the one
who broke it off...
You should ask her.
What are you, an idiot?!
Look, don't yell at me.
What do you expect me to do?
Ayu, it sounds like this
has soap opera
written all over it.
Let's go, Mayu.
We have work to do.
But it's starting to get good.
Ayu!
I know you don't
mean that, Takayuki...
And I know that deep down
you do feel
something for Mitsuki.
Whatever.
You don't seem to realize
she has always loved you.
And because your
stubborn ass refused
to be there for her when
she really needed you...
I slept with her.
I know...
And it's all my fault, right?
Get over yourself!
I saw you laughing and
tickling that girl back there,
so don't try to act
like you're innocent!
You're not making any sense...
Leave me alone.
Mitsuki's gone through more pain
on your behalf than
you could ever dream of!
You're right, man...
she has suffered...
All because of my actions,
and I take full responsibility.
So you realize that yet you
won't do anything about it!
What do you want...?
What the hell am I supposed
to do about it now?
We wouldn't even be in this mess
if you weren't so damn selfish!
The fact is, Mitsuki's
supported you this whole time...
And yet what have you
done for her in return?
Nothing.
Fine, then what do
you suggest I do?!
You need to figure
that out for yourself!
No, Shinji, you're wrong!
It's your turn now.
What are you talking about...?
My turn?
Since you're so insistent
about doing something,
why don't you start
taking care of her?
Come on...
I mean, you are in
love with her, aren't you?
You jerk! I'm not
good enough for her...!
It has to be you!
Don't you see that?!
You're a fool to let a girl
like her get away from you!
You bastard!
That's quite enough.
You're like a disease.
Everyone you surround
yourself with suffers.
Shin... ji.
Hi. It's Akane.
Haruka regained
consciousness yesterday.
We explained to her
that she's been asleep
for three years, and she doesn't
remember waking up before.
She wants to see you.
I know things have
been weird lately,
but if you can spare the time,
it would nice for you to visit.
I have baked the finest
bread for you, my love.
Now let us break
this bread and dine
in the clouds of
eternal happiness!
No, that's not right.
I have baked the finest
bread for you, my love...
Now let us break
this bread and dine
in the clouds of
eternal happiness!
That was it...
Now I can play the leading role.
Sorry to break the
bad news to you...
But the director said
the lead role is mine.
That's not what I heard.
It's mine.