Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
All right,
Mitsuki, looking good...
That was big improvement
since last week.
Remember this feeling.
What's wrong...?
You look so nervous.
Uh... Who are you?
Let's see... seven, seven, five,
six, four, three, and five...
You only got a score
of thirty-seven...
Unfortunately for you
that's far from acceptable.
Whoa, what's far
from acceptable...
and I still don't
know who you are!
I'm so sorry, Takayuki.
Is that your sister?
She's kind of a handful.
I'm Akane Suzumiya...
Nice to meet you.
You're cuter than I expected.
Oh, thanks.
She's not coming
with us today, is she?
No way! She just followed me.
We'll get to be alone...
I think.
Oh, don't worry about me!
Even though it
is summer vacation...
I wouldn't be rude
and tag along...
I'd ruin your hot date.
It's not... hot...
Oh, would you
please just leave?!
Fine, I'm gone...
I'm gonna check out
the boys at the pool.
Oh, wait--
You go sticking your
hands down her pants,
and you'll have to answer to me.
Got it!
Ha...! I made you
blush like a girl...
He's so innocent!
Have fun, you two!
What's wrong with you!
I'm sorry.
She's always like that.
What'd she say...?
I hope it wasn't too crass.
Oh, no. It was nothing...
Living with her must be a
real pain for you sometimes.
More than you could ever know.
Your sister's got
a wild attitude.
I can't peg why, but she kind
of reminds me of Mitsuki.
Makes sense.
She's younger and
less experienced,
but Akane's also
on the swim team.
That does makes sense.
And she usually wins in
the meets she's been to...
She says she wants
to be just like Mitsuki
when she gets older.
Now, that's a
frightening thought.
Are you all right?
Sure, I'm fine.
I was just up late.
Did you get any sleep?
Some. I borrowed a
video game from Shinji...
I was up until dawn.
No wonder you're tired...
You guys and your games...
Are you still studying
for your exams?
Probably not as
much as I should.
I'd love it if you took the
entrance exam for Hakuryo.
Koyou University
is too far away.
I'm afraid of how
much I'd miss you...
Being so far... it'd be hard...
It's not too late,
you know... We'd have fun.
Yeah, we could walk to
and from school together--
I think we missed our stop.
Why didn't you wake me up
at the right station?
You were fast asleep...
and you looked innocent,
like a baby...
I couldn't... You were too
cute to wake up... Sorry.
That's okay...
Don't worry
about it... Let's eat.
Here.
I brought us some really
great food for lunch...
Do you want to sit down?
Excellent!
I was so worried
it would collapse.
Hey! A meat pie...!
Those are my favorite!
I've heard all about
how much you like them,
and I've been practicing
for a while...
I think I got it though.
This is the first one
that's come out of the oven
looking the way a meat
pie is supposed to look.
And it didn't fall
apart on the way here.
I have high hopes,
so tell me how it
tastes and be honest.
Sure.
Well?
It's great!
Really?
Yeah, delicious!
I'm so glad.
I gotta try...
You weren't lying.
This is pretty good.
I like this.
Hmm?
This is nice.
Yeah... it is.
No way!
I just couldn't
believe the guy did it.
I'm not that surprised.
Thanks for walking me back.
Do you want to come inside?
Uh, well... I kinda...
You're just nervous... right?
No... it's not like that...
Hi, lovers!
Akane!
I'm starving.
Are you two coming inside...
Or are you staying out here?
Uh... We, uh...
Dude... Make up your
mind...! Which is it...?!
Three, two, one, answer!
Well... it's late...
and I wasn't raised that way...
It's rude to your parents if
I just drop in unannounced...
So I can't--
You can keep flapping
your gums inside.
Akane, wait up!
Welcome to our humble
abode and excuse any mess.
We weren't expecting visitors.
Takayuki...
You really need to
learn to relax some.
Sure...
Now... Just kick back and eat.
We've heard so many good things
about you from Haruka...
We're thrilled to
finally meet you.
Thanks... Uh...
Stop it...
That's enough, Akane...
I'm sorry about that...
She doesn't have manners.
Now, that that's done, dig in.
So... Mr. Big Brother...
I wonder...
How many dirty thoughts
have crossed your mind?
What?!
I oughta--
Did you call me brother?
Yup... Why?
Because...
No one's called me that before.
I've always wanted to
have myself a big brother...
And while you're
not exactly perfect ...
I'll put up with you.
Thanks... Great.
There's just one thing...
You gotta marry Haruka
before you can be my bro.
Akane, stop acting
like a freakshow!
You two need to
loosen up some...
Takayuki...
All I want from
you is to be nice
to my daughter while
you're dating her.
We can worry about
marriage later.
Yes, sir!
Are your parents cool
with you going to
the festival tomorrow?
Yeah, I had my curfew extended.
But I think we'll be alone.
Mitsuki said she's
too busy to go with us.
Busy?
Do you think she
found herself a guy?
I think so...
At least that's what I hear.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
If she's got a real boyfriend,
that's a first for her...
Hope it works out.
I didn't... expect that.
Akane saw her in town
walking with some guy.
She didn't know who he was,
but he was definitely
around her age.
Ok... I hope she's happy...
Then it'll just be the
two of us tomorrow...
But uh... We can leave
Shinji out of it.
You can't ditch your
best friend like that.
He'll get over it.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hi, this is Takayuki.
I'm out right now or
I'm asleep or I'm busy.
At any rate,
I can't reach the phone.
Leave a message after the
beep and I'll call you back.
Mitsuki!
So were you busy last night
when I tried to call you back?
I guess...
I don't think I ever
heard the phone.
Well, I had three missed calls
from you when I got home.
I got worried. What's the deal?
Oh, nothing.
Fine. I'm lying.
Can we... just talk?
Is this drama about
your new boyfriend?
I don't have one.
I heard you did.
No. We were just hanging out.
And then yesterday
he told me he loved me.
Which I'm getting used to.
But, I still don't
know how to handle.
Are you gonna keep seeing him?
Maybe.
So... What do you
think I should do?
I guess...
if it's someone you're
really into, I'm all for it.
Okay...
I didn't think you'd say that.
You know, he's
like the tenth guy
who's said that to me...
And I've walked away
from every single
one of them who did.
It kinda gets under my skin...
But... I guess
I can't blame them.
Wow... cocky.
Oh, come on...
You know it's true.
I mean, everyone
admires my hair.
But I hate it.
It's pretty and lush and rich,
but it represents the part
of me that I don't want...
The part that's too proud.
But this guy didn't like it...
He's the only one who's told me
I'd look good with short hair.
I don't think
I'll ever forget him.
So what...? Do you like him?
I don't know... I wish I did.
I wish it were an easy decision.
That's it... I'm gonna
turn him down.
I think it's more important
to be true to my feelings,
the way Haruka held out for you.
Sounds good...
You gotta stay true to yourself.
The festival.
Yeah.
But... Haruka?
She'll understand...
You needed a friend right now.
There he is!
Shinji? Haruka?
What are you doing here?
Looking for you... jerk!
You had a date
with Haruka tonight
and you stood her up!
You got some kinda glitch
in your manners?!
I found her at the
festival standing alone
and crying thanks to you!
It's all right, Shinji...
I'm just glad
that he's not hurt.
I'm so sorry, Haruka.
I didn't know that the
two of you had a date today.
I needed to speak with Takayuki
so I brought him up here...
There's been a lot
on my mind, lately...
I'm sorry.
It's okay...
Whatever.
I felt bad about it,
but I couldn't
just ignore Mitsuki...
She needed to talk to a friend.
I don't know what
to say... Haruka.
Don't worry about it...
You're my best friend.
I just hope that when you
feel you need a friend,
you know you can
count on me, too.
I do know. Thanks, Haruka.
Everything's fine.
We all ended up here together,
which is what I wanted
in the first place.
It's just perfect...
I don't think I ever
wanna be away from you guys.
Me, neither...
Well, since we're all here,
let's go to the
festival together...
I've heard it's supposed
to be pretty fun.
Sure, but as an apology
I want to pay for everything.
Sweet, cause I'm broke...
Now what do you say we all
line up for a picture first?
Good idea...
I don't think we have any
pictures of the four of us.
Exactly. And it's about time.
We gotta squeeze tighter.
I'm trying.
Hold still.
I'm sorry about today.
It's all right.
Mitsuki was feeling down,
and you're a good friend to her.
I would have
done the same thing.
Really?
It means a lot to
me that you would
take your time to help
my best friend feel better...
You're a good person, Takayuki.
No lights?
Mom and Dad went out
to some business party.
Don't worry.
Akane went with them.
That's good
So, do you wanna come upstairs?
I'm enjoying talking to you.
Oh... yeah.
Hey, nice room.
I like your computer.
The place is a mess...
Try not to look at
anything too closely.
Look at that.
You've got a ton
of children's books.
You still read them?
Yeah...
Cool.
When I was a kid
I read Mayal's Gift...
But I don't see it up
here on your shelf...
Isn't it kinda rare?
Well, then we should go find
you a copy of it sometime.
I'd like that.
It's my life's dream
to write children's books.
That's why I have
to go to college.
I'm gonna major in
child psychology so I know
just the right things to put
on the page for the kids.
You're amazin, Haruka...
and someday... you will.
When you're a famous writer...
you should write a
book about four friends...
and how close they are.
That sounds nice.
Haruka...
Yes...
I'll go open the
front door, okay?
She's already home?
Sis, are you here?
We're home now!
Akane?
You guys are late.
It must've been a fun party.
So, Big Brother...
Did you have fun rolling
around in the sack
with my sister?
What?!
No...! Now just,
get out of my room!
Busted...
Akane... Tell me something:
Do you like me dating your
sister or do you hate it?
Because you just
can't have it both ways.
Sure I can!
Um, sorry about
the interruption.
Haruka...
We don't need to
rush any of this...
We have time.
I'm not going anywhere.
So, since we're together...
We should make a little wish.
Like this?
That's perfect.
Now keep your hand still
and repeat after me.
Like the brightest stars in
the darkest skies of night...
Hearts that have truly
joined will never fade.
Even, if these hands
ever pull apart...
Even, if these
hands ever pull apart...
The connection between us
will never be betrayed.
I'd love it if you took the
entrance exam for Hakuryo.
You gotta be kidding me?!
Nope.
I'm actually prepping
for the Hakuryo test.
I'm impressed... For real.
It's her, right...?
Haruka's got you.
She does.
Oh, it figures! I'm late!
I hope Haruka isn't mad!
But if she is, she'll
forgive me when I give her this.
It'll go over huge with her!
Takayuki?
Hey, what are you
doing around here?
Mitsuki.
Hey, what's with that
get-up your wearing...?
You got a date?
No... I've just got an outing
with the swim team later.
Sounds, fun.
Will you ever get off my case?
So are you and Haruka
doing something today?
Yeah. I'm supposed to meet her
in front of the train
station here in a few.
It sounds like things are
going well with you two.
I must say I'm jealous.
You should be.
I'm a huge catch...
Well, have fun with all your
swim friends this afternoon...
See ya!
Takayuki... Hold up.
If you didn't know...
it's... my birthday today...
So, I, uh... Just thought...
Oh, this is the one I want.
Right here.
It almost looks like two rings.
So what?
I don't know,
it looks kinda gaudy
for someone as young as you are.
I guess you have a point...
Too much. Okay then...
Let's see...
I'll take this ring, thanks.
Wait, are you sure about that?
It's no fun to get a gift
you don't want
on your birthday...
Geez... Now I'm broke.
Oh, I can't thank you enough...
I'll keep this ring close to
me for the rest of my life.
You'd better...
And for my birthday, I expect
you to roll out the red carpet.
I'm talking caviar, expensive --
Oh crap, look
what time it is...
Uh, I gotta go! Bye!
Ambulance...?
I guess someone got hurt.
Where's Haruka?
I hope she didn't
get upset and leave.
Some young girl
in a white dress.
Yeah... it's too bad.
I wonder if she'll be okay.
That car ran right into her.
Hope she wasn't waiting
for someone. Poor thing.
Haruka...! Haruka!
Haruka?! Haruka, where are you?!
Haruka...! Excuse me, sorry!
Haruka...?!
Are you okay...?! Haruka!!
Time of accident,
two fifteen pm.
I have verified the
identity of the victim,
through her student ID...
Victim is a senior,
at Hakuryo University,
the college feeder school...
Her name is...
Haruka...
Suzumiya.