You guys make me sick.
You ignore my sister
for three entire years
when she was in a coma,
and the whole time
you were hooking up with
each other behind her back!
Tell me... Aren't you
ashamed of yourself...?
Do you feel any guilt at all?
My sister needs you now.
She wants you to be by her side.
Yet you just stand there with
that stupid look on your face.
You're nothing but a coward!
You know I'm glad.
Huh?
Even though the situation sucks,
I'm glad Haruka
came out of her coma.
Yeah.
Wow. It's really
pouring out there, huh?
That was pathetic!
I've seen kids in junior high
swim faster laps
than you just did!
Did you not learn anything
over the last three years?
Well you can kiss that corporate
sponsorship goodbye now.
There's no way they'll want
to sign a fifth place
finisher to a deal.
The real world doesn't
work that easily.
You're not going to have a coach
to hold your hand through life
once you leave this school.
If you're not willing to give
a hundred and ten
percent then move over
so someone else can!
♪ We have strived to do our
best in the halls of Hakuryo; ♪
♪ But now's the time ♪
♪ For us to grow ♪
♪ Into this world,
off we go. ♪
Takayuki! You home?
Come on...
He forgot to lock
the door again.
Wake up.
You need to get some sun
or you'll turn moldy.
I'm guessing you
didn't eat breakfast.
You know, it's a
good thing you have me,
'cause I brought you some food.
I've got to head back to work.
Don't forget to lock up
if you go somewhere, okay.
Oh no...
I'm gonna be late again.
That's all I need.
What's up...? You need
a lift, hot stuff?
Shinji! You have perfect timing!
I'm so glad you saw me.
My lunch hour is over in a few
minutes and I can't be late.
So hurry!
I'm surprised you're
not kissing up
to your boss and
eating at your desk.
What are you
doing driving around?
I thought you
had school today...
Or are you flunking out again?
Don't you wish.
So can I assume that you were
walking back from
Takayuki's place?
Uh, yeah.
If I were you
I'd leave him alone.
Why?
What's it been,
a whole year since that day?
If you keep babying him
he's never going
to snap out of it.
I know Takayuki
well enough to know
that sometimes it's just better
to let him handle it on his own.
I don't agree with that.
Look, he's not a kid anymore.
Just let him deal with it.
Besides, Haruka's accident
was just that--an accident.
It wasn't your fault, Mitsuki.
Yes it was.
Huh?
Thanks for the ride.
You really saved my butt.
Don't work too hard.
Yeah...
I wish I could say
the same to you,
but knowing your work ethic
you'd be expelled by now.
Ah, shut up!
See ya!
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Now...
What amazing dish am
I gonna cook up tonight?
Hey, Mitsuki!
Akane?
So how's school going?
Good, great actually...
and swimming is going well, too.
I'm becoming one of
the fastest on the team.
Really? That's awesome.
How's the rest of the team?
Fine... but, I'm
a little disappointed.
I never knew the
coaches could be
so overtly cruel
to us, it's getting old.
Yeah well...
they may be tough, but it seems
to bring the best
performances out of everyone.
Y'know?
No!
Listen...
They criticized you,
and right in front of me.
They said you don't have
a career in swimming now
because you lost your
edge chasing after a boy...
None of them...
None of them understand.
They just don't get it.
Akane.
Thank you for
everything, Mitsuki.
Huh?
You've been so incredibly
gracious helping with Takayuki.
Oh it's nothing...
I don't mind...
Takayuki's my friend
so I like helping him...
He's been in pretty bad shape,
but I would be, too...
I bet in no time he'll be back
on his feet and feeling better.
Mistuki.
I'm just so happy you're willing
to help my sister and
Takayuki through this.
I know she'll...
I know she'll wake up
one day and be so happy...
Thank you.
You're so nice.
It's okay.
Um, Mitsuki, would it be alright
if I asked you for a favor?
Of course.
Well I have a videotape
of me swimming a
few laps of freestyle...
Would you mind
taking a look at it
and judging me on my form...?
I'm not very good
at criticizing myself.
Sure I will...
Though I'm not sure
how much help I'll be.
Awesome! Thank you so much!
Here you go.
Come on...
How many times
do I have to remind him
to lock the door if he
leaves the apartment?
Geez, what a pigsty.
Perfect.
Better change that bulb.
Mitsuki.
Oh, hold on a second.
I have some soup
I can heat up for you.
Takayuki. Let's go do
something fun tomorrow.
I think it would
do you some good
to get out of this musty
apartment for the day.
Okay.
Huh?
Let's do it.
Oh wow. You've gotta
see this, Takayuki.
It's gorgeous!
I find it amazing they can put
so many different types of fish
in one tank at the same time.
Don't you...?
Wouldn't you think
all the big fish
would start eating
the little ones?
I don't know.
Look...
I paid for your ticket,
so the least you can do is act
like you're having fun, okay?
I'm gonna keep walking.
Huh...? Oh, cool.
Hey...
Uh, what're you doing...?
Would ya let go?
What's wrong?
Oh cool!
Check out those cups!
Don't you think they're cute?
Not really.
Here, buy 'em for me.
What?
Well, come on...
I paid for your ticket;
I'm always cooking for ya.
Well?
Fine.
I'll take these.
Great.
Alright!
It feels good to get out.
Thanks... I had a lot of fun.
Sure.
You wanna grab a
cup of coffee with me?
No, thanks.
I think I'm just gonna
walk around a bit more.
There's a book I wanna find.
Oh okay... I'll call you later.
Sounds good.
I don't believe it.
They're holding another exhibit.
Hi, this is Takayuki.
I'm out right now or
I'm asleep or I'm busy.
At any rate, I can't
reach the phone.
Leave a message after the
beep and I'll call you back.
Hey, Takayuki it's me.
I guess you're not home yet.
If it's alright with you, I'm
just gonna leave this mug...
you know the one you
bought me, at your apartment.
So, I'm gonna come over.
I'll see ya then.
Takayuki?
No, he's not here with us.
Why, what's up?
Oh nothing.
I'm sure he's fine.
He doesn't have a cell phone
so I thought I'd try you.
You should have seen him today.
He was in great spirits.
That's good to hear.
Look, I gotta run, but I'll
let you know if he calls, okay?
Thanks.
Haruka.
Haruka. I saw a poster today
for another children's book
exhibit coming up.
Remember? Mayal's Gift?
The author's going to be there.
You want to go right?
It'll be fun.
What?
You better believe it.
Of course.
Don't worry.
We're not gonna miss it again.
I promise...
I'll even rent us a car.
Yes.
No, I haven't seen
Takayuki here all day.
Thanks anyway.
Visiting hours are over
so if he's coming here
it'll be tomorrow.
Is it urgent?
Oh, no... Just forget it.
Sir, you can't do this!
Put her down! Quick!
Someone call security!
Get out of our way!
I don't think you understand
how dangerous this is!
We have to leave now
before it's over!
We can't miss it! Come on move!
Please! She's only asking
for this one thing!
Move!
Takayuki!
I made a promise to her!
You can't make me break it!
Move!
Get a hold of yourself!
Even if you take her there,
it's not like she'll be
able to see anything.
You of all people
should know that.
She's in a coma!
Haruka.
I feel so bad for
you being stuck
in this awful hospital
bed all the time.
It's not fair to you.
And it's so hard for Takayuki
to have to see you like this.
Why did it have to happen?
Why? If I could go back
to that day, I would...
I would put myself
in your place...
I really would.
Takayuki.
We understand that
you care for our daughter,
Haruka, very much,
and we appreciate the
time you spent with her.
And I know she
appreciates it as well.
And that's why
I'm sorry to say...
Please forgive us...
but we don't want you to
visit our daughter any longer.
I'm sorry, son...
but we're doing this
for your own sake.
Please. You can say
goodbye to Haruka,
but you're not
welcome here anymore.
You're gonna catch a cold.
Come on...
Snap out of it already.
I understand how you feel...
I know it's hard...
It is for me too.
But there's nothing...
There's nothing
you can do about it.
No matter how much
you feel for her,
the fact is she can't return
those feelings to you now.
It's useless to dwell on it...
Takayuki.
Are you even listening?
Ugh! Why won't you say anything?
What, are you dead inside?!
I just want you
to acknowledge me!
Say something!
Wake up!
I love you...
And I've...
I've always loved you.
And I tried to ignore
it all these years...
I tried so hard to bury the
feelings that I had for you.
Because I didn't...
mean to betray Haruka!
But, I can't stand it ...
I hate seeing you like this...
what you're doing to yourself...
what I'm doing to myself...
Do you... love me?
Good afternoon.
It's so blue.
Mitsuki.
I decided to skip work today...
You look hungry.
Let me make you something.
Oh, thanks.
I wonder what ever
happened to Takayuki.
I'll see you when you get back.
Okay.
Maybe he got the
flu or something.
Might as well find out.
Anyone home...? Hello?
It looks like
Mitsuki's here, too.
You... You've been lying
to me this entire time.
Akane.
Look, Honey... The rain stopped.
Space, it is a frontier.
And it is the last one.
Stop it...!
Your hands smell funny!
I don't like all
this space stuff!
What if a scary alien appears!
Fine, then I'll
try something else.
Spaceship Sky Temple
with Captain Ayu
Daikuuji on board...
Try again!
Geez! All right.
The future of mankind...
No!
What is your problem?!
Wait, don't press that!
Oops.