[EREN whimpering]
Damn it!
[ARMIN] And just like that,
everything changed.
At that terrible moment,
in our hearts, we knew.
Junior High was a pen.
The students, cattle.
[EREN growls]
Damn you, Titans!
You okay?
This isn't over.
I'm going to the
Titans' building
to get our cheeseburgers back!
[ARMIN gasps]
[MIKASA exhales]
How exactly you s'posed
to pull that off?
Me too--!
[NILE]
Are you out of your minds?!
Get inside! Immediately!
What?! So the school
just turns a blind eye
and pretends like
nothing's wrong?
Am I correct to assume
you're Eren Jaeger?
According to my records, you
pledged to follow the rules
of this institution,
or don't you recall?
I'm not about to just stand
here and let those monsters--!
[WOERMAN] Quiet! Either
you'll do as you're told,
or we'll kick you out!
Ugh! Go back to class--
[YMIR]
Whoopsie!
What the--?! That's in...
[groans]
Guys! Stop it!
What're you doing?
No! Wait! They'll throw
the book at you!
[WOERMAN gasping]
You little delinquents!
As of this moment,
you've all jointly committed an
offence punishable by detention!
Make a run for it, Eren.
I owe you one. Thanks!
[ALL gasp]
[EREN panting]
[MIKASA] What've I told you?
Where you go, I go.
[ARMIN]
Same with me!
[JEAN] Joined the party.
Ugh, this is stupid.
More like scary!
I just wanna go home!
[CONNY] Eh, it's no big deal.
What the hell, right?
[EREN]
You guys!
[MIKASA]
Yeah, yeah. So what's the plan?
I say we head for
the Scouts' clubroom.
The upperclassmen will know
what to do, I'm positive!
[NILE] Damn it!
You come back this instant!
[KEITH] Grisha. Today
should bring you pride.
Your son is a warrior!
Bad news! The Titan's raided--!
You don't have to shriek, moron.
We saw the whole thing
for ourselves.
[EREN]
Good!
So the Scout Regiment
plans to retaliate, right?!
For now we're on standby.
[EREN]
What?!
[LEVI] Whatever you
think it is we do here.
A big part of it
involves keeping
our gut reactions in check.
That's what keeps you safe.
Oh, come on!
Our only shot at getting
the chee-burgs back
is if we get off our butts!
[PETRA]
Eren! That's enough!
[EREN] We just sit around and
wait for this to blow over?!
We're gonna let the Titan's
do whatever they want
without even putting up a fight?
And if we do?
Now stop whining and
show some respect!
Why are we all ignoring
the obvious?!
Bullies count on us not doing
anything! Unless we--!
[ORUO] "Ask not the reason why.
Ask but to do and die!"
You'd understand what those
words mean i f you weren't
such a craven jack-a-napes!
[EREN growls]
I guess if the Scouts
made themselves known,
then they'd be disbanded.
Or even worse.
If we don't keep a low profile,
we might get expelled.
[EREN]
No.
I can do this without them.
It's time for me to stand
on my own two feet.
No, stop! Don't do it, Eren!
[EREN gasping]
[LEVI]
I wouldn't blame you.
[EREN, PETRA gasp]
Do whatever you think best.
Truth is, I don't know which
is better. Never have.
Should I go with my gut?
Or put myself out there
and give my classmates
the benefit of the doubt?
There's no guarantee
either way. In the end...
...you choose what you choose.
If afterward your regrets
are minimal, great.
[PETRA]
Eren.
Just trust us.
Go on! Make up your damn mind!
[EREN]
I'm gonna do it!
[ALL gasping]
[EREN grunts]
[ARMIN]
Eren!
[JEAN]
Wait up!
[SASHA]
Don't leave me!
[CONNY squawks]
Somehow I always figured
I'd come back to this place.
This is it, people.
The Titan Building!
Yeah. Here I come, you bastards,
to drive every last one of you--
[screams]
[ALL screaming]
This was the worst idea ever!
[EREN] Aw, crap! Why didn't we
think to bring the ODM gear?!
[HANNES]
Eren!
This way!
[HANNES]
You kids all right?
[EREN gasps]
Mr. Hannes! Rico!
Thought you'd need this.
[EREN]
Seriously?!
Wow! You're awesome!
Wait, you...?
You're not gonna tell us to
stand down, or whatever?
Yeah, no,
the Titans helped themselves to
our kamameshi without asking.
It's now or never.
They need to learn not
to mess with humans!
Yeah, they do.
[RICO]
Plus, it's good publicity.
Wall Cleanup Club membership
will go through the roof!
That's your reason?!
[HANNES]
Here's the deal.
Wait for an opening, then
move it. I'll distract them.
You gonna be okay?
Cut me some slack.
It's what I do.
"Janitor" is just a role.
Now go get your
cheeseburgers back!
Mr. Hannes!
[HANNES]
Yoo-hoo!
Low hangin' fruit for
the picking, boys!
[HANNES groaning]
C'mon. Follow my lead.
[HANNES]
Pay attention, Eren.
At the end of this hallway
is the principal's office.
There's a door in there
you'll need a key to unlock.
That's where your
snack stand is.
No question.
This is it!
Now it's real.
The principal's office!
[ALL gasping]
I mean, I didn't think it'd be
normal size, but holy crap!
Okay. Right, let's go!
Somewhere in there
are our chee-burgs!
So, where's the key?
Yeah, or for that matter,
where's the door?
I say we check out the desk.
[EREN yelps]
What the hell is this?!
[RICO] What's a whole
city doing in here?
[gasps] You guys seeing
what I'm seeing?!
[CONNY]
There it is!
[SASHA]
Look! I think that's a keyhole!
Eureka! I think I know
what we have to do!
We have to get the key
into the lock somehow!
[IAN]
Uh, heads up! Incoming!
[SASHA]
We left the door open!
[CONNY]
Four Titans! Ten meters high!
Eren, you make for the key
and get it to the keyhole!
Everyone else, back him up!
Do what you can to see this
mission through to completion!
[ALL]
Roger!
This is it!
We're actually doing it!
[EREN grunts]
What in the hell?!
I can't get the damn
thing to move an inch!
[ARMIN screams]
What's going on down there?
What is he doing?
[ILSE] There they are.
You're getting all this, right?
Yep. Just do your thing.
Ilse Langnar reporting. Tonight.
Titan's running amok
at the festival.
It was a day like any other,
and like a bolt out of
the blue they came:
huge, lumbering terrors
making off with the students'
beloved snack stands.
A handful of brave souls
are retaliating,
but will the fight
be for naught?
[EREN grunting]
[ARMIN]
Eren! Hurry!
What're you guys doin' here?
The only way out of this for
any of us is out of this city!
[MIKASA]
Uh, oh.
I'll help Eren work
the key free!
You handle the Titan!
Whatever you do, keep him away!
[MIKASA]
On it!
[ARMIN] Eren. We're getting
our chee-burgs back.
Say we're getting
our chee-burgs back!
I want you to be honest with me!
Even though coming
here meant the difference
between the classroom
and hell on earth.
Even though it meant risking
detention, or worse.
Why throw caution to the wind
and venture into
the Titan Building?
What kind of question
is that? Don't play dumb.
You know damn well why.
Because. Those cheeseburgers
are my birthright!
[CONNY gasps]
What the--?
[CONNY gasping]
Not on my watch, Titan!
Ow!
Jean!
Get out of here already!
[TITAN D groans]
[JEAN]
Whoa!
Wait, aren't you--?
[JEAN gasps, screams]
[FEMALE TITAN A]
Blush.
What's gotten into Eren?
[JEAN]
Mm?
[SASHA gasps]
[CONNY]
Uh...
[EREN]
I feel like...
like I'm about to buckle
under the weight.
Eren!
[ARMIN]
Mikasa!
[MIKASA]
Uh! What happened?
He got it out somehow!
He-He's determined to see the
mission through to the end!
As long as we've got his back
while he heads for the keyhole,
victory will be ours!
[IAN]
Defend him!
[SASHA, CONNY gasping]
[IAN] To the last man if
that's what it comes to!
Eren must reach that keyhole!
It looks like we're back on!
Focus on keeping Eren safe!
Pay attention! You'll miss me!
[EREN]
We're born free. All of us.
Some don't believe it.
Some do whatever they
can to take it away.
To hell with them and the
rules of Attack Junior High!
Fight.
Fight!
[MIKASA]
I'll take care of it!
[RICO]
Out of the way!
[JEAN]
I am not going to die today!
Go!
[EREN yells]
[EREN]
Fight!
Dude, you did it!
You got the door open!
[EREN] Well, c'mon.
What're we waitin' for?
Let's get in there and
take back what's ours!
[RICO]
Comrades. Your sacrifices....
weren't in vain.
But, no one actually died.
There's the stand!
It's right on top!
[ARMIN] They're keeping our
cheeseburgers in a gym?
You bastards! Give them back!
[MIKASA]
Eren, wait!
No!
[ALL screaming]
[TITANS grunting]
[ALL groaning]
Um, I think this is what they
call "the end of the road."
[EREN growls]
What do we do now?!
--[rock music plays]
--[STUDENTS gasp]
Okay, piglets. On your knees.
♪ When the wall comes down  ♪
♪ At the end of town ♪
♪ And you're someone
else's meal, ♪
♪ I'll pummel through,
through the future ♪
♪ Close the suture.
All You gotta do is kneel! ♪
Bravo!
That's cool!
Aw, they came!
Huh. What d'ya know?
Wow. No idea who they are,
but I'm glad they showed up.
[SASHA, ARMIN, CONNY]
Uh...
What?
Whoa, how can you seriously
not know who that--?
[ALL gasp]
[CONNY]
Uh! What's that?
[ARMIN] No! That's impossible!
That wall has to be...!
[EREN]
Oh, god.
It's him!
Oh crap!
I was wrong. We're not in a gym!
This is...
the principal's lunchbox!!
Hey! What are you doing?
Put that down!
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[EREN] This is our chance!
Don't let it slip away!
[EREN grunts]
Hi there.
Haven't seen you since
the entrance ceremony.
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[gasps]
[EREN]
Stop!
Oh, no!
[ARMIN] Hurry, Eren!
Save the chee-burgs!
[EREN]
That doesn't belong to you!
Uh?
[ARMIN screams]
No way is he good for that
thing's digestive system.
This isn't real.
[ALL]
He spit him out! Eren!
[EREN]
Guys. I did it!
I got a chee-burg back!
[ALL cheering]
Oh, man. What a relief!
For a second there I
thought he was a goner.
[CONNY]
Awesome!
He actually did it!
And his eyes are saying
"check me out."
Oh, Eren.
No two ways about it:
gross disobedience!
These, idiots flew in the face
of the principal himself!
[ERWIN]
I don't disagree,
but I feel this establishes
a fine precedent.
One I'm eager to see the other
human students follow.
Never before today
did any of us imagine
we could go against
the Titans and win.
On the surface, this may have
been about cheeseburgers,
but on a deeper level
it's about hope.
Gentlemen. I believe we need
to reconsider the rules.
Perhaps even overhaul them.
We want the students
to be safe, of course,
but we also want
them to have fun.
This time, it's
our turn to attack!
[ALL]
Chee-burgs!
Chee-burgs! Chee-burgs!
[EREN]
Yes!