[STUDENTS chattering]
[CHRISTA]
Hey, Annie!
Uh. Huh?
What's your favorite
thing to eat for lunch?
If you don't mind me asking.
[ANNIE]
I really like cheese--
[NACK]
That chee-burg bastard
from the other day
was hilarious.
No kidding. I mean,
when's the last time
you've seen someone our age
into cheese Hamburg steak?
Right?
[BOTH laughing]
[CHRISTA]
Um, hello?
Annie? You okay?
Uh!
You were about to say
"chee" something.
[THOMAS]
What'cha talking about?
[NACK]
Yeah.
Uh, actually I think
you heard me wrong.
[ANNIE]
I said seaweed.
[STUDENTS]
Huh...?
Wow! As in mozuku? So grown-up!
[EREN] Tomorrow's the big
dodgeball tournament!
[ANNIE grunts]
Yeah! We're gonna kick
some major butt!
[ANNIE]
Is that a fact?
[EREN]
Hm?
I make you this promise
right here and now.
Tomorrow, I will personally
obliterate you.
Consider yourself warned.
What's the deal with her?
Listen up, people!
There are fewer things in life
more important than dodgeball!
We win this, the
Class 4 First Years
will be the coolest
kids in school!
[JEAN] And my association with
the winning team will earn
yours truly substantial
props with the ladies.
[GIRLS]
Ah! Jean, you're so amazing!
[JEAN] According to the rules,
everybody has to participate.
We all in? Right!
So begins the saga
of my rise to the top!
Wait. Armin, where's Eren?
Um, seems he overslept.
Damn you eternally, Jaeger!
This was supposed to
be my moment to shine!
Pretty emotional
day for him, huh?
Whatever. He totally loves it.
Right. Keep it together, Jean.
Just, cover up that
Eren's not here.
Would anyone care
to explain to me
what this racket's all about?
If I didn't know better,
I'd say it had something
to do with the fact
that Jaeger appears
to be absent.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[MIKASA]
Eren's in the restroom,
and the racket is
because Sasha farted.
[SASHA]
Ah!
Why doesn't that
surprise me?
[SASHA] Ah! Misaka! Why
would you say that...?
[KEITH] For crying out loud,
girl. Learn some restraint.
[JEAN sighs] Good save!
He was completely sold!
[KEITH]
In the meantime,
if I catch any of you slackers
goofing off even a little bit,
I will personally hand-feed
you to the Titans myself.
[STUDENTS scream]
[KEITH]
Hmph.
[JEAN]
Well this just got real.
Okay, team, are we
all in agreement
that we cover for Eren until
the jerk decides to show?
Damn right!
And remember, we're
playing this to win!
[STUDNETS]
Yeah!
All right, let's get this
dodgeball tournament under way!
The first match'll be
'tween Class 4, Team A.
And Class 1, Team B!
Ready? Let's see some
sportsmanship!
Best of luck, and play ball!
Mine! Ha!
[CONNY grunts]
All right!
[JEAN] Conny's a moron,
but he's a born athlete.
If he keeps this up, he'll be
our first-string offense!
'Kay! Heads up!
Boosh!
[TOYOHASHI]
Uh.
What the hell are you doing?!
That's the other
team's outfielder!
D'you even know how this
game's supposed to work?
Oh, sorry.
Tell me what we're
playin' again?
[TOYOHASHI grunts]
[CONNY]
Uh.
[MARCO]
[HANNES]
Conny and Marco are out!
Dodgeball.
You're supposed to hit the
other team's infielders.
[CONNY]
Right. What are infielders?
Well I guess that'll teach me to
underestimate Conny's stupidity.
Hey, on the bright side
at least now we know who
the weakest player is.
We can make do...
[ARMIN]
Sasha, no! What are you doing?!
[SASHA] What do you
mean what am I doing?
I'm eating ramen!
[ARMIN]
I can see that!
Why eat it here of all places?!
[SASHA] You expect me
to let it get cold?
That'd be a total
waste of good ramen!
[ARMIN] I think you kind of
might be missing the point!
[JEAN yelps]
Got it! Ha!
Oh, no! Sasha, look out!
[SASHA]
Oh!
You're kidding me. Take this!
Take that!
Of course!
Nobody separates Sasha
from whatever she
happens to be eating!
[JEAN]
Which would be awesome
if she didn't have
to use her hands!
This is embarrassing. Don't
we have one decent player?
Wait, there's Mikasa!
She's got skill!
[grunts]
Ha, ha!
No way a throw that lame's gonna
tag out somebody like Mi--
Come on! Seriously?!
You're that weak?!
Yeah. The thing about Mikasa
you have to understand
is that when she's separated
from Eren for too long,
her stats go down by 30%.
What?! How is that a thing?
[MIKASA]
The world is a cruel place.
[ARMIN] Hard to believe a girl
just out of elementary school
can go that dark.
[JEAN]
What it with this team?
An idiot who can't get his
head around the rules.
A girl who stuffs her face
in the middle of the game.
And our star player:
whose depression is so
intense it's got an aura.
[growls] What is going
on with this team?!
[JEAN] Ugh. Okay, the first
match is in the bag.
but I wasn't counting on it
being such a struggle to win.
Right? Imagine if Mikasa
was in top form.
[sneezes]
[JEAN] Hey, what
happened to your futon?
[ARMIN]
Uh. She took it.
Fantastic, girl's gotten worse.
Sorry. I have no idea
what else to do.
She's just...
[HANNES]
Okay!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[ARMIN]
Looks like Annie's team is up.
Uh-oh.
Whoever wins this match
is our next opponent.
[IBATA grunts]
[CHRISTA yelps]
Christa, no!
[YMIR grunts]
[REINER groans]
She's perfectly safe, thanks.
How can I ever repay you?
How 'about when this crap's
over and done with,
you marry me?
[REINER growls]
Gettin' tired of this!
[gasps] Annie! Look out!
[BERTHOLDT]
No! [groans]
[ANNIE]
Huh?
[REINER]
Annie! Heads-up!
What the--?
[STUDENTS scream]
Reiner!
[REINER yells]
Take this!
[STUDENTS scream]
[whistle blows]
[HANNES]
Game over! Class 4, Team B wins!
[ALL scream]
We don't... We don't
stand a chance.
It's as if they're a hive mind.
Well, yeah. It's what
teamplay's all about.
Every member's in tune
with each other.
And they don't eat ramen
in the middle of a match!
[ANNIE]
Where's the chee-burg bastard?
He'd better crawl out from
whatever rock he's under
before our match starts.
Or else I'm telling
Mr. Keith on you.
Heh.
[JEAN]
Uh! Uh... Well, that's it.
There's no way
around it anymore.
We're gonna be
five-star Titan chow.
Ugh! Come on, Eren!
Help us out here!
Wake up already!
[EREN]
Crap!
[HANNES]
Lunchtime! Eat up, kids!
Hey, Annie?
I was wondering if you'd
mind me asking something.
Are you really that
into mozuku seaweed?
[ANNIE gasps]
Why does she want to know?
Is she baiting me into
admitting the truth?
Uh. Yeah.
Love it.
I was hoping you'd say that!
I have some for lunch today,
but I think it's gross.
I was sort of thinking
maybe you'd take it
so it wouldn't go
to waste, you know?
For a second there, I thought...
You know, what? Sure.
[STUDENTS]
Annie.
While you're at it, would
you mind eating my mozuku?
Mine, too, please?
--[THOMAS] And mine!
--[MINA] Same here!
[BERTHOLDT]
I hate the stuff, so...
What's wrong with you people?!
Seaweed tastes good!
[JEAN]
We're in big trouble.
S'only a matter of time before
we're eaten. Trust me.
[sighs] Why couldn't I have
done more with my life?
If I'd known it was just gonna
end up like this I would've--
[ARMIN]
I've got a plan!
[JEAN]
Uh...
Dead ringer!
It's too perfect!
[JEAN] You're out of your minds!
I don't look anything like Eren!
Uh, actually, your
physiques are similar.
You both have the
face and shifty eyes
of your classic bad guy.
Say that again!
I think the two of you look so
much alike it might even manage
to pull Mikasa out of
her weird little funk!
It won't. I can't
feel his spirit.
[ALL groan]
Huh. Okay.
That doesn't sound like
a crazy person at all.
[ANNIE]
Pardon the intrusion.
[ALL gasp]
[ANNIE] It's almost time for us
to get this match under way.
Chee-burg bastard
better be here.
[SASHA] Don't you worry about
that! Eren's right here.
Wait a second,
something isn't right.
When did you get horse-faced?
[JEAN whimpers]
What's your favorite thing
to eat for lunch?
[JEAN]
Hm? Om-nom?
[ARMIN]
Dang it!
Uh! Oh, hell!
[EREN]
Chee-burg!
[ALL gasp]
[EREN panting]
Sorry, guys! I overslept!
Cuttin' it kinda close there!
[MIKASA]
Get out of my way!
[ARMIN]
Futon!
Mikasa!
Now that I'm here,
everything's gonna be--
Tardiness is a very bad habit.
[EREN]
Yes, ma'am.
Glad you decided to
show up, Chee-burg.
Prepare yourself to
be squashed flat!
Bring it on, Annie!
This team's not afraid of you!
Time for the
championship match!
Right!
Class 4, Team A will
go head-to-head
with Class 4, Team B!
So, is everybody ready?
And begin!
[REINER]
Got it!
Annie?!
[EREN] Leave it to me,
everybody. This one's mine!
[EREN yells]
Ugh. Seriously?
[gasps]
[HANNES]
Eren is safe!
Wow, she's so agile!
Yeah. Quite the
difference, huh?
Glad Eren showed up.
I'm just gettin' started!
[ARMIN yelps]
[HANNES]
Safe!
This time...! [groans]
[HANNES]
Safe again!
[MIKASA] Whoever comes
at Eren, deals with me.
I don't care what they
try to throw at us.
[HANNES]
Eren's safe.
[ANNIE grunts]
[EREN yelps]
[HANNES]
Yep. Safe.
Still safe.
He's getting blasted,
but he can't get out.
Mikasa's catching the rebounds.
Whoa. This is painful.
Ow.
[HANNES]
Oh, uh, Jean's out.
[EREN groaning]
[THOMAS]
This is insane!
They're the only three
left in the game!
I'm about to end
this in one throw!
[ANNIE] Do it.
Let's see what you've got.
[EREN yells]
[ANNIE grunts]
Wow. That was some
serious skill.
It's a special technique.
If you want, I'd be
happy to teach you.
[EREN]
No thanks. Dodgeball hurts.
Are you kidding?
Stop trying to be
so damn modest.
[MIKASA]
Hey, Annie.
[ANNIE growls]
I wanna learn your technique.
Teach me.
[ANNIE]
I'm not so sure about that.
Whole thing only works
with human beings.
Uh, oh. Epic match alert.
Hell yeah!
Double or nothin' Mikasa
kicks Annie's butt!
I bet my strawberries!
Cool. I bet herring.
And I'll bet my meatballs.
I'm in.
Let's do it.
Come at me with all you've got.
[MIKASA grunts]
Let me get out of the--
[EREN groaning]
[MIKASA]
Eren!
Annie. Why do you
hate me so much?
It's not like I've ever
done anything to you.
Heh. You really wanna know?
[ANNIE sighs]
Pay attention,
'cause I'm only gonna
say this once.
At the entrance ceremony,
you told everyone you loved
Cheese Hamburg Steak.
Without even realizing it, you
basically stole my thunder.
It was my favorite first!
I should've been the
one to blurt it out!
So naturally I hate
your Chee-burg guts!
I don't understand.
Couldn't you have
just said, "Me, too?"
[gasps]
Uh?
Look, I'm really sorry.
When you get right
down to it, though,
we have something in common.
[ANNIE]
I suppose we do.
That's sweet. Yay, friends!
Huh?
[REINER]
Mm-hm.
Huh?!
This is some BS.
[HANNES grunting]
Wait, what's going on?
I get it now! Dodgeball!
I totally just tagged her
out, right? Huh? Huh?
[whistle blows]
[HANNES]
Technically, yes.
Game over. Congratulations.
[MIKASA, EREN, ARMIN]
Let's dig in!
All right! My fav!
This isn't happening!
That was my chee-burg
for the day!
[MIKASA]
No three-second rule.
[EREN gasps]
[ANNIE]
Mind if I join you guys?
Hey! Sure, no problem!
[ANNIE sighs]
Is that..?
Yeah...
It was gonna be the best part of
my whole lunch, except now...
We'll share.
Uh! No way! Really?
Thank you!
Best Chee-burg ever!
That was super nice of you!
Meh. Whatever.
In return, though.
Let's agree to, uh, forget
what I tried to pull--
Eat this.
You're not getting enough
fish in your diet.
[EREN]
Mikasa, stop it!
I'm not your little brother and
I'm not some snot-nosed toddler!
[MIKASA]
Eat it!
I'm not about to let you
get malnourished!
[ANNIE]
Here. Have another one.
[EREN]
No joke?
[MIKASA]
Hey!
Not until you eat some
of your vegetables!
You can't survive on
Cheese Hamburg...
Quite the one-eighty.
I smell a Love Triangle!
[ARMIN]
Wall Cleanup Club.
Eren and the others show
up for their first day
not knowing what to expect.
In truth, nothing could've
prepared them.
At first, they thought their job
would be a normal one.
Then they showed up.