[ARMIN]
Summer.
Temperatures are on the rise.
More and more people
wear short sleeves.
It's early in the season,
but tensions in the
classroom run high.
Soon, the other shoe will drop.
Every student's fate hangs
precariously in the balance.
[KEITH]
All right, maggots.
Listen for you name.
To the morons out there who
tanked, bear this in mind.
Makeup exams'll be next week.
[ARMIN] The dreaded day of
Test Results is upon us.
[KEITH]
Next up, Armin Arlelt!
Yes, sir!
[KEITH]
Perfect score!
[STUDENTS]
Whoa!
[ARMIN chuckles nervously]
[KEITH]
Now we have Sasha Braus.
[SASHA]
Uh! Yes, sir.
[KEITH]
The hell are you doin'?
[SASHA]
Huh?
I said: what the hell
are you doin'?
[KEITH]
Congratulations, young lady!
You are now officially
on my bad side. Again.
[SASHA sighs]
Seriously, tell us your secret.
If I bombed as many exams
as that, I'd lose my mind.
There's gotta be some trick
to how you're still sane.
That's harsh, man.
Says the guy who got all zeros.
How are you not totally freaked
out about what's at stake?
If you flunk the make-up tests
you're banned from lunch
for the rest of the semester!
[SASHA screams]
[SASHA]
Eren! You've gotta help me!
Stay and be my study
buddy, I'm beggin' you!
Love to, but I'm headed to
the Scouts' HQ, so... Bye!
Mikasa?
[MIKASA]
I'm with him.
[SASHA]
Sure. Go ahead.
You I'm not even
gonna bother to ask
'cause I know you'll be a jerk.
Way to make it a lot less fun!
Somebody step up
and be the hero!
If I fail the makeup
tests I'm doomed!
[BERTHOLDT]
Um. Sasha?
I'll be glad to help you--
They're never gonna let me eat
lunch at this school again!
[CONNY]
Okay, okay. Fine.
What's the trick to getting
the perfect score, you ask?
Well, it's hard to say.
I've got kind of a gift.
It's all about feelin'
it, y'know?
You got straight zeroes
on everything.
Ah-ha! Armin!
Help me! Come on!
You got all perfect scores!
You want me to help you
study? Sure, no problem.
You're a life saver!
Oh, I'm happy to lend a hand.
You can join us, too,
if you like, Conny.
[CONNY]
You mean it?
And all of a sudden,
I'm confident we're being
steered in the right direction!
Yeah! When we put
our heads together,
the sky's the limit!
Hooray teamwork!
Right! Those tests won't
know what hit 'em!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[CONNY]
Let's do it!
--[SASHA] Study buddies!
--[ARMIN] I believe in you!
All righty, then.
Let's get started.
Wait. Where'd Conny go?
[SASHA] Uh, he was standing
right here, wasn't he?
How'd he even...?
[CONNY humming]
[ARMIN]
Did he honestly forget
what we just talked
about and head home?
[CONNY sighs]
I love this time of year.
[ARMIN]
Okay, then.
Well let's not worry
about him at the moment
and instead dive right
into your weakest subject.
Okay!
That would be math.
Definitely a foreign
language to me.
[ARMIN] Hm. Let's see here.
Take this problem.
I suspect that the letters
tripped you up here.
Try substituting X
and Y in your head
with an apple and an orange
and see if that doesn't help.
Solving for letter
values is way easier
if think of the equation
in terms of food.
So let X be apples
and Y be oranges.
[SASHA]
Heh...
You see what I just did there?
Now the problem's
more relatable.
[laughing]
Wow! This is working
like a charm!
So basically we've been sitting
through algebra all this time
just to figure out the
market value of produce.
Oh, man.
If I'd have known it was
all about consumerism,
I'd have grown my own.
Whoa! Okay!
Getting' a little too off track!
It's was just an example!
Tell you what:
let's dial it back.
X and Y can be whatever
you want them to be!
Whatever I want them
to be? Like what?
Uh well, for example...
X can be steak. Y can be curry.
Why not go five-star dinning?
Hold up!
So X is boiled eel
and Y is pickled plum?
Sure thing!
Or X can be tempura
and Y can be watermelon?!
Of course!
Why did I never realize
something as boring as math
could be the stuff
dreams are made of?
You see?
Algebra can be magical!
[ARMIN]
Just not in the way you think.
Thank you, Armin!
With this method I can solve any
problem the test throws at me!
Yeah! That's the spirit!
You've just got to
believe in yourself!
Oh, and in real life,
avoid all the food combinations
we just imagined.
[SASHA]
Uh.
[EREN]
Ah, ha, ha, ha!
Scout Regiment, here I
come, to do Scout stuff!
Will you stop running
like that, please?
Afternoon, everybody!
[PETRA] Oh, hey First Years.
How's it goin'?
[ORUO]
Ugh! Damn it all! Why?
What am I supposed to do?
How was I supposed to
know it'd come to this?
Stop it. We talked about
this. You're whining.
Is something going on, or--?
Don't!
Oh, my. I didn't
want to mention it,
but since you asked,
I have to expound.
[PETRA growls]
If you must know,
I did poorly on the tests
recently administered...
[PETRA]
No one cares.
...which I'm honor-bound
to tell you
is the source of
my current distress.
Do not be deceived, greenhorn!
What?
My failure gives you
no right to disrespect--
[ORUO groaning]
Hey. Are you okay?
Apologies for making a scene.
The pecking order is important,
the rookie has to
know his place.
You just confused him.
[ORUO]
Hmph! Indeed so.
Our exchange went
exactly as planned.
Ugh. What happened to you, Oruo?
You never used to
talk like this.
Look, it's none of my business,
but if you're trying to
be like Captain Levi,
it's kind of embarrassing.
You're not him.
Never will be. 'Kay?
So 'less you wanna
come off like a poser,
I'm gonna need you
to use your head.
Ha, ha.
If you intend to hound
me like girlfriend, Petra.
There's rather more of me you
need to be acquainted with
before laying claim
to the privilege.
[PETRA] Next time you bite your
tongue, I hope you bleed out.
[JEAN]
What's the big deal?
So your test scores aren't
the greatest. Who cares?
[ORUO]
Oh, please!
For your information, plebian,
test scores are not
the issue here.
I'm ashamed for letting
my guard down
and performing less than
admirably on something
at which I'm known to excel.
Ha! Not that I expect you
to understand, of course!
And why, you ask, don't I
expect you to understand?
Because when push
comes to shove,
you're as far from
my level as can be!
I don't even study.
Did you know that?
I ace my exams
purely on instinct!
[JEAN]
This guy!
Hey!
What did I just tell you about
trying to imitate Levi?
Stop. You're only making
a fool of yourself.
Oh, and by the way,
we know you study a lot more
than you'd like us
to think you do
'cause I talked to your
mom the other day.
She says the night before
a test, you're frantic.
Sweetheart?
I made you a snack.
It's late.
[ELD] She's brags about
you all the time,
says you're the most
conscientious student
in the whole world.
'Course I guess you could
be deceiving your own mom.
Ugh! Unbelievable!
You realize that's just
like spying on me!
Are you all so desperate?
Why do you even care about
my test scores to begin with?
Fine! I suppose you'll
stop at nothing!
Like I said, no one cares.
Humph. How can I possibly
fight such persistence?
So be it, then. I'll let
you see how I did.
But only on condition that I get
to see your test scores as well!
[ALL]
Huh?
Wow, guess we're
really gonna do this.
Whatever. All right.
[ALL]
One, two.
What?!
Wait a second.
That doesn't look bad.
[ORUO]
Are you kidding?
I missed a perfect score
by six whole points!
[PETRA, EREN]
Huh?
You First Years have no idea
how good you have
it come test day.
I'd offer to let you tutor me,
but you seem woefully
under-qualified.
I'll just ask a teacher.
You set us up so you could
rub it in our faces!
[HANGE laughs]
Levi!
[HANGE]
Tada!
What do you say whoever
did better on their test
treats the other to some
yakisoba bread, huh?
Shut up.
[HANGE]
Huh?
Ah, ha! I'm just kidding!
Yeah! Only havin' a laugh!
But actually, there is something
we need to talk about.
I happened to be starving
at the moment,
and wouldn't you know it,
not even enough in
my wallet for crumbs!
Come again? The ol'
conscience weighing on you
for not treating your
pal Hange to a meal
you know she needs and would
be eternally grateful for?!
You've got enough
for Sacchan Squid.
[HANGE]
Huh?!
News flash: Sacchan Squid
is not, nor has it ever been,
yakisoba bread, and you're
a monster for implying
they're in any way similar!
Stop trying to
sidestep the issue!
[LEVI] So you make a bet
with me knowing your score.
Then you go and jump
all over my case
for making an
alternative suggestion?
I'll chalk this one down
to stupidity and move on.
I'm sorry. I'll admit
my bold-faced attempt
to finagle you into buying me
a piece of yakisoba bread
was somewhat questionable,
if not downright dishonest.
However!
Huh?
However. Nothing ventured,
nothing gained.
[LEVI]
Starve for all I care.
[HANGE]
Have it your way!
I'll just exploit the Levi name
to leech our underclassmen!
FYI: You're a stupid jerk
and you have stupid hair!
[LEVI] You really need to
work on your comebacks.
[sighs]
[JEAN, EREN panting]
[LEVI]
What are you people doing?
We had to... she was
out of control!
Crazy girl just shows up out of
nowhere and went on a rampage!
Please, sir! You've gotta
get her out of here!
[LEVI]
Yeah, no.
[EREN]
But Hange was hardcore flailing!
You should've seen it!
She took out Oruo!
[LEVI]
Good for her.
See?
You were an absolute fool
to underestimate me.
Let it be known that
Hange plays for keepsies.
Let there be no doubt you're a
few sandwiches shy of a picnic.
[HANGE sighs]
[EREN] Uh... Not that
it's any of my business,
but how'd you let yourself
get so short on cash?
Gah! Idiot! Shut up!
[HANGE]
Ah. I knew it.
You possess a singularly
curious mind, don't you?
[EREN]
Well. I, uh...
[HANGE]
You ask questions! Oh, ho! Yes!
All the sordid details
fascinate you, huh?
[EREN]
Hange.
What, uh, what'd you bring us
to the science lab for exactly?
Well, we of the Biology Club
use this room from time to time,
with the faculty's blessing, of
course. Welcome to what we do!
'Kay. Seems a little bit...
I dunno, dark?
Now allow me to
introduce to you!
[EREN]
Ti... Titans?
Aren't they just adorable?
I've had these li'l darlings
for a while now.
I still need to come up with
suitable pet names for them,
though. Something cute,
along the lines of "dung
beetle" or "sea urchin."
We gotta do this again?
Her naming scheme is so freaky.
Ah! You're "Sawney."
And we'll call you "Beane."
Let's be chums, huh?
[MOBLIT]
Hange, please! You're too close!
[HANGE]
Hm?
Whoa-ho! That was a close one!
That's what I just told you!
You can't treat Titan's
like hamsters!
[HANGE]
Of course you can!
We've been fumbling in
the dark for too long,
the framework through which
we understand these creatures
is built on little more
than fear and contempt!
I concede that my approach may
be a complete waste of time.
However. Nothing ventured,
nothing gained.
[moaning]
[HANGE]
Mm? Go on. Talk to me.
Oh!
Hange! Will you
please stand clear?!
[laughs] You were just a hair's
breadth from getting me there,
weren't you, darling? [laughs]
Argh! You're gonna get
your head chomped off!
[HANGE laughing]
[LEVI]
I see how it is.
This pretty much explains
why you're broke.
[EREN]
When did you come in?
Exactly right!
The cost of feeding
them is enough to keep
our club's finances in the
red! I try to scrape together
what I can, but my allowance
is a joke, so, you know...
[stomach growls]
Guess it can't be helped.
Levi.
I am not treating you. I except
to be paid back in full.
Levi!
[LEVI]
Here.
Uh?
[HANGE]
What's this?
Food for your hamsters.
Not for her?!
Go buy some Sacchan
Squid for yourself
and leave me alone.
[HANGE] Gee, thanks.
You are one stubborn bastard.
[ARMIN]
I'm so proud of you, Sasha!
You got most of
the answers dead-on!
Well, I did have a
pretty awesome tutor.
Hey. No, at the end of the day,
you accomplished
this all by yourself.
[SASHA] If I'm honest, I always
thought Armin was a total wuss.
But he's also a sweetheart.
And so intelligent!
In fact, he's all
kinds of wonderful!
[SASHA] Thank you. I'm really
grateful for the help.
[ARMIN]
Oh, it's my pleasure.
Good luck on the makeup
tests! See you tomorrow!
[SASHA]
You're amazing.
You didn't have to help me out,
but you stepped up.
Now it's my turn!
Ha! Yeah!
Uh?
[ARMIN screams]
The street is pitch black!
[SASHA]
What's gotten into you?!
Scared of the dark!
[ARMIN whimpers]
[SASHA laughs]
[SASHA] To be fair,
he's still a bit of a wuss.
[KEITH]
All right, livestock!
The remedial tests
are in front of you!
Try not to screw it up!
And begin!
[SASHA]
It's got an X and a Y!
And I know exactly what to do!
Ha ha! You don't scare
me, algebra! Huh.
So, what should I substitute?
Well, steak and curry
sound marvelous,
but Hamburg steak and
melon are also good.
Or I could go with cake,
sushi, gyoza, pizza,
bean-paste bun and ramen.
Ah... What's on the menu today?
[ARMIN]
In the end,
Sasha got the same grades
on the makeup tests
as she did the
first time around.
Now she's in remedial classes.
[CONNY humming]
[HANGE laughing]
Yahoo!
[MOBLIT]
This is dangerous!
[ARMIN] Conny was automatically
put in remedial classes
because he forgot about
the makeup tests.
[CONNY]
Ah! Favorite time of the year.
[ARMIN]
Popularity.
Jean dreams of it,
lives for the day when
girls fall at his feet.
A certain something
found in his locker
might just bring that
day a little closer.