[ILSE]
My name is Ilse Langnar.
Today, after school, I witnessed
the Student Council president
doing something terrible.
First and foremost
a journalist,
I'm racing toward the Newspaper
Club's HQ as I write this!
The wrongdoer must be exposed!
I will not yield.
I will not yield!
[ILSE gasps]
[ILSE screams]
[HANGE]
Sawney!
What have I told you
about wondering off?
[LEVI]
Can we go back inside now?
Hey, what'cha got
there, captain?
Huh. Looks like Ilse
Langnar's battle record?
[HANGE] Well, it's only courtesy
for Sawney to return it.
[ILSE screams]
[BOY STUDENT A] The school
newspaper's got balls!
[STUDENT B] They sure put the
student council up a creek!
We have to hold elections for a
new student council president?
[JEAN]
Heh.
[ALL chattering]
[SASHA] I can't believe
you're serious, Jean.
So, you're really gonna to run?
Uh, yeah. Sure! Why not?
What the hell else you think my
achievements have been building
to this whole time?
Am I right, Marco?
Ah, sure'd be nice for all
the hard work to pay off.
Such an honor to serve
your classmates.
[JEAN]
Come on, man! Drop the act.
We're not in elementary
school anymore.
Please. Politics are how
you get the womenfolk
to stand up and take notice.
But that, that's not
what I'm all about.
Once I've become president,
the ladies will fall all over
themselves to get with me!
Plus, I'll be livin' easy
'cause there ain't squat to do!
[laughing]
Wait. We talkin' student
council president?
If I'm elected,
the Titans will pay!
I'd be in a position to drive
every last one of them out!
[REINER]
Sorry, my bad!
What? Say that again freak!
Or don't bother to
'cause it's obvious I'm
the one the people want!
Yeah, dream on, pal!
Nobody gives a crap
whether or not you
get to live the easy life!
[REINER]
Sorry! My bad again!
I've had enough of you.
[EREN yells]
[JEAN grunts]
[JEAN, EREN groan]
[EREN]
Oh, gimme a break...
[JEAN]
Yeah, that's what I thought!
Let Mikasa save your butt!
She's sure isn't gonna
win you the election!
[MARCO] Wow. Didn't realize he
was this interested in politics.
When I win, I'll
get my own Mikasa!
[MARCO laughs]
[MARLO]
Dammit. This is crazy.
To think the council was betting
on beetle sumo wrestling.
[HITCH]
I guess the corruption
ran deeper than any of
us dared to imagine.
I mean, that is why I joined
in the first place.
I just didn't know scandals
would be so much work.
I joined because I wanted to
reform the system from within.
Oh, you're that guy.
Well good on you, Marlo.
Bravo. Want me to recommend you?
I didn't say that to get
your nomination, Hitch!
Yo, feel free to chime in.
Ew, gross! She sleeps so weird!
I'm Jean, and I nominate me!
[MARLO, HITCH]
We've got a live one here.
[HITCH] I need your
signature first.
[JEAN]
Oh, I see how it is.
Already want my autograph, huh?
[HITCH]
Huh?
So, when you look at
me you see a winner?
[HITCH groans]
I'll tell you what, sweetheart.
I'll go one better and give
you my email address--
You have the face of a horse!
[EREN]
Uh. Hey, Marco. Where's Jean?
Oh, uh. He had to stop
by the nurse's office.
I'm on the way to grab
his campaign posters.
Huh? We need campaign posters?
Don't worry! I've got this!
We can make some at my place!
[EREN]
What are we waiting for?!
Thanks, Marco!
[ARMIN]
Why don't we try this layout?
[EREN] That's fantastic!
You're a total pro!
Ha, ha. It's not that hard,
really. Matter of fact,
heh, if you're game, I can make
some tweaks to your face.
Awesome! Do what you
gotta do, man.
Just make me look cool!
[ARMIN] No problem.
We'll move these here.
[EREN] Perfect! And... maybe
do something about that?
[ARMIN]
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
[EREN] Oh! And make
that part really pop!
I'm talkin' like,
you know, buh-bam!
[ARMIN]
Sure.
[EREN]
Yeah-ah! Now we got a poster!
Okay.
You're, uh, gonna put up
that where people can see?
Well, sure! I wanna
get elected, right?
You think it's awesome?
Be honest.
[ARMIN]
Mikasa. Please.
Tell him how you really feel!
[MIKASA]
Uh. I think it's fine.
[ARMIN screams]
[EREN] I'm gonna tell
everyone you designed it!
Oh, you don't
need to do that.
You don't even need
to put 'em up.
Are you kidding?!
These make me a shoo-in!
[MARCO]
Hey, Eren.
[EREN]
Marco!
Guess you guys got
your signage made.
[BOTH]
Copy cat! Mine go up first!
Whoa!
What the hell?!
[ORUO]
Oh, that's cute.
You're still trying
to distribute media.
[EREN]
Of course, but..!
Don't tell me you're running!
[ORUO]
Naturally.
[JEAN]
That looks nothing like you!
[ORUO] You're wasting time,
boys. Peddle elsewhere.
[JEAN, EREN]
Huh?
This bulletin board
has all it can handle
advertising yours truly.
The others are already
filled up, too, I'm afraid.
There's nary a free space
on campus! Sorry!
[EREN growls]
Then what do we do?
[ORUO] Hm. And here I thought
you wanted to be president.
Figure it out.
[JEAN, EREN]
Got it!
[ORUO]
Hm?
[EREN, JEAN]
We'll just put 'em over yours!
[ORUO]
Over my dead bo--!
[ARMIN] The results of
the opinion poll are in!
[EREN]
What?! Oh, come on!
Zero percent's quite an
accomplishment in its own way.
[HANGE] First time I've seen
someone poll so badly.
[EREN growls]
Don't even--!
Hange!
Hey. Stop making so damn
much noise out here.
Ugh!
There has to be some way to turn
this thing around in my favor.
[HANGE]
Possibly.
[JEAN, EREN]
Huh?
Yeah. The reporter
who broke the story
on the student council
brouhaha is named Ilse.
You should try talking to her.
She keeps a notebook.
Rumor has it
there's some pretty
down-and-dirty stuff in
there about this school.
And it really exists?
Has anybody ever
actually seen it?
You have, right chief?
Yeah. And it covers
everything: The dirt.
The grime.
The nitty-gritty.
I'd kill to have it.
So if I was to get
my hands this thing,
I'd have a pretty baller
political weapon, huh?
[LEVI]
You could say that.
[JEAN] Heh. Marco!
To the Newspaper Club!
[MARCO]
What? Wait a minute!
I don't think so! Hey!
You're not gonna get
the drop on me!
[REINER] Move it, Bertholdt!
That's notebook's ours!
[BERTHOLDT]
It is?
No running in the
hallway, dumbasses!
[RICO] And if I am elected as
your student council president,
I promise you
right here and now.
The wall will shine
like a new gold coin!
[ILSE]
Rico Brzenska.
Platform: to increase spending
on Wall Cleanup efforts,
to reinstate the draft.
Promote greater awareness
of custodial duties.
[JEAN]
There she is!
[ILSE]
Hm? Two more candidates.
Eren Jaeger and Jean Kirschtein!
[JEAN] Hand over your
weapon immediately!
Wait, my, my what? Huh?
The magical notebook
belongs to me!
Wha-what in the
world's going on?
[JEAN]
Gimme gimme gimme gimme!
[REINER] I'm gonna be
student council president!
[IAN, RICO]
Uh.
[EREN, JEAN]
Hold it!
Argh! What is the issue
with these people?!
[JEAN]
I'll never catch her like this!
The presidency is mine!
[ILSE panting]
[ILSE]
My name is Ilse Langnar.
While on a routine
fact-finding mission,
several candidates
for the office
of student council president
started chasing me.
My future seems dubious.
However, if I can manage to
reach the Newspaper Club's HQ,
there's a chance I'll survive.
In my shoes,
a normal person would shrink and
cower in the shadow of fear.
But I will not yield!
I will not yield!
Give it here!
[CONNY]
Much obliged, Jean!
Conny?!
[CONNY] Following you was
the best idea I ever had!
[JEAN]
No fair! You can't play dirty!
[CONNY]
Uh?
[ALL scream]
[SASHA]
Yeah!
Sasha!
Give back my notebook!
Hey! I called dibs, damn it!
[SASHA]
Oh that's cute. Sorry, Jean!
All's fair in love and politics!
I call first come first serve!
Now let's see.
Wait, this is...!
I got it, Bertholdt! Run away!
[BERTHOLDT]
Done!
[JEAN]
Stop!
[ILSE]
Give me back my notebook!
[EREN]
This really sucks!
D'you have a stomachache
or somethin'?
I've just discovered something
that will change my life.
All my wishes are about
to come to fruition!
On Wednesdays the cafeteria
gets massive supply
of yakisoba bread!
Aw yeah!
[MARCO, MIKASA grunt]
Where is everybody?
[REINER] Come on, Bertholdt!
Get the lead out!
[JEAN]
Stop, you bastards!
[ILSE]
Give me back my notebook!
[MIKASA grunts]
Mikasa!
[BERTHOLDT] Heads up, Reiner!
Mikasa's on our tail!
Eren! Grab it!
[EREN yells]
[RICO]
Move aside!
[EREN groans]
[RICO grunts]
Eren!
For your information using the
ODM gear counts as cheating!
This is for the sake of
the Wall Cleanup Club.
Uh!
Just as I thought.
You've all been duped.
There's no secret weapon
for winning this election.
These are just cleaning
instructions.
And very thorough ones,
I might add.
Not exactly what we expected,
but probably something
Levi would kill to get
his hands on, I suppose.
What?! You're kidding me!
[ILSE]
What is wrong with you idiots?!
[MARCO]
We're very sorry.
[ILSE] You all've got
some serious problems!
Don't be too hard on 'em.
Deep down they're nice people,
just sometimes a little on
the impulsive side, y'know?
Actually.
They're kinda painfully honest.
But, that makes for
a good president.
[ILSE]
Huh.
[HITCH]
Competition has been fierce,
given the surprising
number of candidates,
but as we bring this battle
royale to a close,
let's give our presidential
hopefuls a final word!
All right!
Which of these people
will you chose to serve
as Attack Junior High's
Student Council President?
First up to make her last speech
is candidate Rico Brzenska!
And, if I'm elected,
not only will this school
be so spotless
you can eat your lunch off
the floor, every student
will be conscripted
into doing their part
to keep it that way. Yes, that
includes working on weekends,
but the extra effort
will be worth it!
[STUDENTS]
Boo!
[gasps] But, I...!
Well, she gets my vote.
[HITCH]
This is democracy!
Next up to the podium
is Reiner Braun!
Comrades! This is
why you want me!
[STUDENTS]
Yeah!
[REINER] If elected, fitness
will be my number one priority!
Attendance at school swim
meets will be mandatory
to increases chances
for physical contact!
[GIRL STUDENTS]
Boo!
[BOY STUDENTS]
Yeah!
[REINER]
Hm?
You pig.
[REINER yells]
Candidate Braun is withdrawing
from shock, apparently.
Our next speaker
will be Oruo Bozad!
Give him your attention, please!
[inhales, groans]
Mr. Eren Jaeger will take
the microphone next.
[EREN]
Hmph.
Look, just promise not
to say anything weird.
Meh. Relax.
My reason for wanting to be
your elected leader is simple.
When president, hm, every last
Titan in Attack Junior High,
no, the world,
will be destroyed!
[JEAN] Nice. The idiot
just dug his own grave.
[STUDENTS]
Boo!
Eren, why?!
[EREN groaning]
Wha-What did I even say?
[ARMIN]
I need to say something!
Wait, what're you doing?
[ARMIN] I haven't had a chance
to collect my thoughts yet,
but I can do this! I'll just
have to think as I talk!
Listen! Eren's not the
moron he sounds like!
If we take his conviction
and combine it
with our superior
intellect and manpower,
I believe we can reclaim
this campus for humanity!
Does this mean we won't
have to give the Titans
our lunches anymore?
Because I'm all for that.
He doesn't know what
he's talkin' about.
[ARMIN]
With our very survival in mind.
In what time I have left
before they kick me off stage,
I will advocate Eren
Jaeger as president!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[JEAN] This is nuts!
The crowd loves him now?
[cheering continues]
[panting]
[EREN] I should probably
keep my mouth shut, but...
I wasn't finished
with the speech!
[EREN]
You... You're cowards!
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
You're all cowards! Just shut
up and put your faith in me!
Hey! What'd you call me?!
[EREN groans, screams]
No!
That's how you figure on
getting yourself elected?
Uh. All right!
Next up is our last speaker,
you'll be glad to know.
Candidate Jean Kirschtein, yay.
[JEAN] They've listened to one
stupid speech after another.
Expectations are at
an all-time low.
This is my chance
to bring it home!
[JEAN]
Fellow students,
I'm gonna be completely
honest here.
I wanna be popular
with the girls.
[BOTH]
Uh...
[STUDENTS]
Boo!
What? What'd I say?
[JEAN]
Why did we do this?
If we'd have known what
we were getting into,
we would've never run.
We've been put
through the ringer,
and all we have to show
for it is regret.
[MARCO] Don't get mad at
what I'm about to say.
[gasps]
Jean's not what you'd
call a standup guy.
But, doesn't that kind of
make him more relatable?
I mean, he's like most of
the folks in this room,
'less I'm wrong.
He's one of us. He gets
our point of view.
That's right.
Jean Kirschtein is a realist.
Personally, he's where
my recommendation goes.
[clapping]
This man's name is Marco Bodt.
And he happens to be exactly
what I'd call a standup guy!
There was nothing
in this for him.
He was just speaking
out for a friend!
Look at the facts! Think!
Who better to serve
as our president?
I tell you this:
I can't recommend
Mr. Bodt highly enough!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[BOTH] How did this happen?
Outdone by Marco?
That's ridiculous!
This can't be legal!
I've been robbed!
I demand a recount!
[ARMIN]
The school festival.
Amidst a snack alley
bursting with goodies,
Eren devotes himself
to cheeburgs.
Moved by his friend's passion,
Armin prepares to sacrifice
something precious.