[HANGE]
Attention!
I'd like to take this moment
to congratulate everyone
on their top-notch performances
in the recent Sports Day games.
And, thinking back to
what brought us there,
ruminate on the fact that
you kids picked a fight
with your upperclassmen.
All in the past now,
but in the interest of your
team-building skills,
we have a li'l event planned.
Something I call....
The Test of Courage!
[ALL]
Huh?!
[EREN]
Look at this place.
It's like after dark it goes
from being a normal school
to the set for a horror
movie or something.
[ARMIN whimpers]
I'm afraid of the dark.
You freak out way too easily.
[EREN whimpers]
What is it you think
you see there?
[ARMIN yelps]
[ERWIN]
Sorry. Didn't mean to scare you.
[ARMIN, EREN, MIKASA gasp]
Hello. I'm Erwin Smith.
The Scout Regiment's
faculty advisor.
[EREN] Uh. I thought this club
was supposed to be a secret.
[HANGE]
Oh yeah! This guy!
Actually, we have this
man's influence to thank
for giving us access to
the building after hours!
By "influence,"
we mean he had to slip
us the key in secret.
Enough with the formalities!
Let's get this party started!
Eren, Jean, Mikasa,
Conny and Armin
will begin at the stairs on
the right side of the school.
Ymir, Christa, Sasha,
Reiner and Bertholdt
will begin at the
stairs on the left!
[LEVI]
Right. The objective is simple.
This is a test of nerve.
You will visit the art,
music and science
rooms, in that order,
leaving your names written
on the chalkboard.
Pretty straightforward, 'less
you got the mind of a child.
Firsts Years are first and we
meet in the gym afterwards.
Anybody need clarification
on the rules?
Uh?! How come we have to go
before the upperclassmen?
Aw c'mon, man, don't
tell me you're scared?
Hey! Shut your face!
Unlike somebody,
I'm not just doin' this
so no one'll figure out
I'm a 'fraidy cat!
What a coincidence.
Neither am I.
Guess that's something we have
in common, huh? Whaddaya know?
I'm afraid of the dark,
I'm afraid of the dark.
If you're too scared, it's no
big deal for us to go first.
It's okay, Christa. Stay
close, I'll keep you safe.
I'm afraid of the dark,
I'm afraid of the dark.
[EREN]
Uh. All right, people!
Let's do this!
Quit waving the flashlight
around. Keep it steady!
[EREN]
It is steady, quit bein' a wuss.
[JEAN]
You're the wuss!
[EREN]
And you're a horse face!
[JEAN]
That's hurtful!
Huh Took 'em long enough, huh?
Don't most people put the fear
of ghosties and ghoulies
behind them once they
reach middle school...?
[ERWIN]
Okay, kids. This is it.
Commence the Attack Junior
High Scout Regiment's
customary initiation.
Let's welcome our new members
with the 57th Test of Courage.
All units, forward!
[ALL]
Shhhhh!
[EREN]
Huh. Looks empty to me.
Ha! I'm gonna be the
first to write my name!
[JEAN]
The hell you will!
[groans]
[gasps] When were they here?!
[JEAN] At least my name will
be on here before yours!
[EREN]
I called dibs, you jerk!
Hey, while you're at it,
write my name up there, too.
[GIRL laughs]
[BOYS gasp]
[CONNY whimpers]
[ARMIN]
Please. D-Don't tell me. Oh god!
It's the Seven Wonders
of Attack Junior High,
Number One: "The
Laughing Mona Lisa!"
[BOYS scream]
[screaming continues]
You know, it's kinda weird.
What's up?
Girls, man.
I mean, why they gotta go to
the bathroom in big groups?
Beats me.
[REINER]
Huh?
[BERTHOLDT]
What's wrong? What d'you see?
[REINER]
Hm... Nah. Never mind.
[laughs]
[REINER]
Hm?
[CHRISTA]
Sorry that took so long.
Hey. Doesn't one of
the Seven Wonders
have something to do
with the bathroom?
I remember! Third stall
door from the right.
They say if you knock on
it three times after dark,
Hanako will pop out
and drag you inside.
Um, don't test it, please.
Come on, nothin'll happen.
See? Just a story.
[FRIEDA]
Who is it?
[GIRLS scream]
[GIRLS screaming]
[YMIR]
Ah! Have no fear, my darling!
I'll protect you at any cost!
That's a promise! A vow!
When all this is over,
we'll get married!
Didn't know you felt that way.
[YMIR screams] Christa
transformed into Potato Girl!
What have you done with
my precious bride-to-be?!
[BOYS panting]
Our t-t-test of courage
isn't going so well.
[EREN] Wait, what is that
supposed to mean?
If you s-s-see all of
the Seven Wuh-wuh...
If, you see all Seven Wonders.
You'll b-b-basically
be c-cursed for life.
It's some seriously bad juju.
Wait, like bad enough to mess up
my popularity with the ladies?
Hold on a sec!
I think that might be the reason
I've been tanking on
all my tests lately!
[JEAN]
Yeah, sure.
Not 'cause you're
an idiot or anything.
[BOYS scream]
What the...?
It's the... the s-s-s-se...
It's the Seven Wonders of Attack
Junior High, Number Two.
Beethoven's 5th Symphony,
played by the ghost
of the composer himself.
[ORUO chuckles]
[BOYS scream]
[ORUO groans]
[EREN whimpers]
[MIKASA]
Eren! Uh?!
[ALL]
Please... don't go...
[MIKASA]
Eren, wait!
[EREN screams]
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[BERTHOLDT]
Hey, Reiner. Notice anything?
Like what?
[BERTHOLDT]
I dunno, man.
Like maybe how these stairs
seem to keep going up?
[REINER]
It's your imagination.
[EREN panting]
Way to go, Eren. Nice
job there. Gold star.
Just had to split
off from the group.
Uh?! Ah!
Oh, it's only me.
What the hell's a mirror
doing here, of all places?!
What the--?
[EREN] That wasn't real! My
mind's playing tricks on me!
I definitely did not see a
creepy girl with long black hair
floating by in the reflection!
It's all in my head!
[GIRL screams]
[EREN screams]
Uh? What's going on?!
[EREN groaning]
[footsteps]
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[EREN]
Ah! Oh, Mikasa, it's you.
[MIKASA]
What just happened?
[EREN]
Nothing!
I tripped and fell down
that stairs, that's all!
I, uh, definitely did not see a
creepy girl with long black hair
floating past me in the mirror!
[gasps] This isn't good!
You suh-suh-saw...
You saw the Seven Wonders
of Attack Junior High,
Number Three.
A cursed infinity mirror
hung in the staircase at
the second floor landing.
If you muh-muh-make
eye c-c-c-contact--
[MIKASA] If you make eye contact
with the ghost who haunts it.
[ARMIN]
Sh-sh-she'll d-d-d-dra...
[MIKASA]
She'll drag you in.
[CONNY] Anybody else
impressed that Mikasa knows
what Armin's trying to say?
[EREN screams]
I told you nothing happened!
I fell down the stairs!
[MIKASA]
Eren! Slow down!
[EREN] ...no creepy girl with
long black hair in the mirror!
And even if there was, I didn't
make eye contact!
[GIRL laughs]
I'm telling you. Something
just isn't right about this.
[REINER]
I don't see it.
[BERTHOLDT]
Seriously?
We've been climbing these
stairs for like thirty minutes.
[REINER]
It's your imagination.
[BERTHOLDT] You keep
saying that. I don't think so.
[REINER]
Trust me.
[YMIR]
Christa!
[SASHA] Stop running!
I don't want to be by myself!
[BERTHOLDT]
You're not tired yet?
[REINER]
Imagination.
[CHRISTA cries] Ymir! Sasha!
Where did you guys go?
[CHRISTA]
Ymir?
Whoa! What's wrong with you?!
[EREN] Doesn't look like
Reiner and the others
have been in here yet.
Kind of bizarre.
You'd think we would've
run into them by now.
Muh-maybe they fell
victim. To the...
[MIKASA] Maybe, Reiner
and the gang fell victim
to Wonders Number
Four and Five.
That's The Dancer as well
as a ghastly specter
known as Screaming Skeleton.
Cut it out.
You think I want the back
to be all stretchy?
Stop tuggin' on my shirt!
Hey! You're the one tuggin'
on my shirt, doofus head!
[BOTH gasp]
[JEAN, EREN scream]
[ARMIN, CONNY scream]
[ALL scream]
Gah! What in the hell's
wrong with this school?!
What're you talking about?!
I didn't see anything!!
So, uh, exactly how many
Wonders have we seen?
We're totally gonna be
cursed for life, aren't we?
Yeah. Wuh-wuh-wuh-wuh-wuh.
We're pretty much
done for, I'm afraid.
There's no hope for us.
[YMIR]
Christa! Christa!
[SASHA]
Will you please slow down?!
[JEAN] Why're Sasha
and Ymir on their own?
[BERTHOLDT]
See what I mean?
These stairs just keep going.
[REINER]
It's your imagination.
[BERTHOLDT]
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but this building only
has three floors, right?
There's no way we haven't gone
up several dozen by now.
[BERTHOLDT]
Huh?
[FRIEDA] Ah. So, you got
separated from you friends.
Yeah. I'm scared
and I'm all alone.
Uh? Now, now, you shouldn't
let your nose drip like that.
It's unbecoming of a lady.
You're too cute not to be a
lady. Here, blow into this.
[CHRISTA grunts]
Oh! There, you're
all better now.
A word of advice?
You, uh,
shouldn't walk around
by yourself at night.
Heh. Not unless you want to
end up like me, that is.
How come?
What's so bad about you?
You seem nice!
Yeah! As a matter of fact,
when I grow up, I think I
want to be exactly like you!
No! Don't say that!
Stay just as you are!
[CHRISTA laughs]
[YMIR]
Christa! Christa!
[CHRISTA gasps]
Ymir!
My Christa!
There, there. It's okay.
Oh, right!
This is my friend Ymir
I was telling you about.
Uh?
[EREN]
Hey!
[CHRISTA]
Uh? Hi, guys!
[EREN] Uh... Where's
Reiner and Bertholdt?
Right. Be careful.
Something seems off.
[BERTHOLDT]
Yeah.
[REINER, BERTHOLDT scream]
Now, now. Dry those tears, huh?
But, I... You were...
C'mon! Let's go!
[JEAN]
We finally made it.
[ARMIN yelps]
The suh-suh-sixth--
[MIKASA]
This is Number Six.
A terrifying
apparition called...
[ARMIN whimpering]
[MIKASA]
The Headless Dribbler.
[ALL scream]
[ORUO]
You are all doomed!
[PETRA]
Doomed!
[GUNTHER]
[ELD]
Doomed!
[ALL scream]
[THIRD YEARS]
You are all doomed!
[FIRST YEARS screaming]
I don't see anything!
Not the Mona Lisa,
not Beethoven,
not the Screaming Skeleton.
In fact, nothing out of
the ordinary at all!
You can hear them, right?!
What are you talking about?
I don't hear anyone moaning or
chanting "you're all doomed"
over and over again!
Please! You can so hear them!
[CHRISTA, ARMIN crying]
[FIRST YEARS screaming]
[THIRD YEARS moaning]
What now?!
[REINER, BERTHOLDT scream]
[ALL scream]
[screaming continues]
[ARMIN] Help me, help
me, help me, help me!
Grandfather, take me to my room!
[ALL screaming]
[screams]
If any of you idiots wet
yourselves, I swear.
[EREN]
Levi?
Oruo?
[PETRA] Aw, dang it.
He didn't bleed out.
[EREN]
You did all this?
Well, duh. It's called acting.
[HANGE]
Bravo!
[EREN]
You were in on it, too?!
Sure! Kinda got away from
us there at the end,
but I def helped set things up!
Okay, either you guys
are some serious
special effects wizards,
or you practice black magic.
And whoever you got to
play the Lady in White
was totally on point!
I had a feeling this
was a prank! Ha, ha.
Lady in White? What are
you babbling about?
Sorry, sweetie. Wasn't us.
[EREN]
Uh?
No. You saw The Seven Wonders
of Attack Junior High,
Number Seven.
They say long ago, on a
night light tonight,
a young girl disappeared
during the Test of Courage.
Condemned now to
wander the halls
not even realizing
she's a ghost.
What is it you think you saw?
Ah! I keep telling you!
I didn't see anything!
[screams]
[EREN] Damn it, Mikasa!
Why'd you do that?!
[MIKASA]
Mosquito.
[EREN]
Overkill!
[ARMIN] All he wants is to be
side by side with his love.
Put up to it by Reiner
and the others,
Bertholdt takes his secret
crush to the next level
and asks Annie out to
the Summer Festival.