[ARMIN] And just like that,
everything changed.
At that terrible moment,
in our hearts, we knew.
Home was a pen.
Humanity, cattle.
[MIKASA]
Eren.
Eren!
Come on. It's time to get up.
[EREN groans]
Mikasa?
[MIKASA]
You overslept.
[EREN]
I'm up. I just... I dunno.
It's like the dream I was
having went on forever.
It's gone now.
What was it about?
Eren, are you...
[EREN]
Hm?
[MIKASA]
Are you drooling?
Also, we're late.
[EREN yells]
[MIKASA ]
We'll see you later.
Right. Study hard, okay?
[MIKASA]
Eren. Hurry up.
Bye mom. See you tonight!
Have a good first day of school.
[EREN panting]
Come on!
I can't be late our first day!
Hey, Mikasa, I need you to
swear not to tell anyone
you caught me drooling
in my sleep!
I swear.
I won't tell anyone you put your
pants on backwards either.
[EREN]
Ah! Don't remind me!
[MIKASA]
Look out!
You need to watch
where you're going!
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[EREN gasps]
[CHRISTA gasping]
My bad. I was in a hurry.
Uh. That's okay.
I guess I was, too.
Uh?!
Oh, no! My breakfast!
[YMIR]
Hold up, Romeo!
Bumping into my precious Christa
while she's got
toast in her mouth
so you've got an excuse
to put the moves on her?!
[CHRISTA, EREN gasp]
What "moves"?
Everything's gonna be all
right now, sweetie-pie.
Whaddya say we get married
after the entrance ceremony?
Look, I gotta go.
Have breakfast on me, okay?
Keep your filthy hands off her!
[EREN]
Guess I'll see you around!
[YMIR] We never want
to see your face again!
[CHRISTA]
What am I gonna buy with this?
[EREN panting]
C'mon! Pick up the pace!
[SASHA]
Mm?
Ah! My watermelon!
You eat that for breakfast?
Sorry! My fault!
Here, take this!
[SASHA]
Hm?
[SASHA] This doesn't buy
me another watermelon!
[EREN panting] Okay.
Not gonna run into anyone--
Let's just go.
[MIKASA]
Wait up!
Give me a break!
How far away is this school?
[MIKASA] Huh. Maybe if
I bumped into him...
[EREN groaning]
[MIKASA]
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Sure, yeah.
[CONNY]
Coo, coo, coo.
That's what pigeons
say. Coo, coo--
Uh?
[EREN gasps]
[EREN groans]
Eren.
[EREN screams]
[MIKASA]
Hey! Wait for me!
[CONNY]
Huh?
[EREN screams]
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[YMIR]
You dirty SOB!
[CHRISTA]
Ymir! Slow down!
[SASHA] You owe me
another watermelon, pal!
--[JEAN] What's going on?
--[EREN] This is the place.
[EREN]
Attack Junior High School!
[CONNY]
It's gigantic!
[ALL gasping]
[bell tolls]
[EREN]
Crap! We're late!
[MIKASA]
Eren, wait!
[CHRISTA]
Uh-oh.
[SASHA]
What about my watermelon?!
[gasps] That way!
[SASHA]
Could you slow down, please?
[EREN panting]
[SASHA cries]
[CONNY]
It's gigantic-er!
[CHRISTA]
Yeah. And kinda creepy.
[EREN]
Uh... Come on!
[footsteps]
Uh, so...
Anyone else feel like
something's off?
No. What are you talkin' about?
Seriously?!
Nothing about this
place strikes you--
Ah! There we are!
Year 1, Class 4. That's us!
Please tell me whoever expects
us to open this door's
off their rocker.
'Cause otherwise I'm just
too thick to see...
Will you just shut up and
help us think of something?
Over there.
[ALL gasp]
[ALL]
Whoa!
[EREN] Uh... We might
be the first ones here.
This still doesn't
feel weird to you?
Ugh! Why is everyone so--
[EREN groans]
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[EREN groaning]
[JEAN]
Is that an eraser?
[EREN grunting]
You're not hurt, are you?
It's about to be a rubber stamp!
[MIKASA]
Stop.
You need to calm down.
Something's definitely
not right.
Ugh! Stop being so paranoid!
[EREN yelps]
[YMIR, CHRISTA, MIKASA gasp]
[EREN screaming]
What's goin' on?
[gasps]
No! A Titan!
[EREN]
Titans.
No.
A titan took something
away from me.
Something precious.
[EREN] I! I will erase every
last one of their kind!
[ALL gasping]
[SASHA] What is this?!
What's happening?
[JEAN]
Don't you get it?!
We've wandered into one
of their classrooms!
[CONNY yelps]
[ALL scream]
[HANNES]
Hey!
Darn brats!
What do you think you're doing?
[EREN]
Mr. Hannes!
[HANNES laughs]
Well that was a disaster.
[SASHA] There's nothing funny
about what we just went through.
[HANNES]
I'm sorry, kids.
That was the Titans'
building back there.
You guys are supposed
to be in this one.
[ALL]
Whoa!
[HANNES] Welcome to
Attack Junior High School!
[JEAN]
It's... normal.
[KEITH]
Attention!
All right, class.
Here's the breakdown.
You are all now in
the 104th First Year.
This is Class 4 Homeroom!
Allow me to introduce
myself: I am Keith Sadies.
And you will grow to hate me.
As your teacher, I do not
welcome you warmly!
Right now, you're nothing.
Less than nothing.
Matter of fact what most of you
are right now is livestock.
Nice to meet'cha.
[KEITH] Followed closely by
worthless and pathetic.
Now stand up and say
your names, maggots!
My name is Christa Lenz!
Hi everybody!
I'm Ymir.
[CHRISTA gasps]
And if any of you scumbags
lay a hand on my Christa,
you're dead meat!
Uh. Wall Maria
South Elementary.
Name's Annie Leonhart.
Real great to meet you all.
I'm Reiner Braun.
You're up, cue-ball!
Tell us who you are!
[CONNY]
Me?!
Uh, I mean, sir! Right.
Conny Springer, Wall Rose South
District Ragako Elementary!
[CONNY groaning]
Huh. Let me ask you question,
Conny Springer.
They teach you what side the
heart's on there in Ragako?
Who's next?!
[BERTHOLDT]
I am, sir!
I'm... Bertholdt Hoover.
Very glad to be here.
[KEITH]
Next!
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna say I won't yield
to the Titan scourge.
I want everyone to know I'm
gonna drive every last...
You're up.
[KEITH]
Next!
Sir!
I'm Eren Jaeger, sir!
From Shinganshina Elementary!
And why'd you come to this
school, Eren Jaeger?!
To drive them out! All of them!
And not just from
this Junior High.
But from the entire world!
[HANNA]
Heya, Franz.
Did he actually just say he's
going to drive out the Titans?
Human beings can't defeat
those things. There's no way!
What's with those two?
Couple of pessimists?
That's not exactly
the issue here, Eren.
[JEAN]
Heh. Well then,
every class has a weirdo.
Guess we know which one's ours.
Me? I try to steer
clear of the Titans.
I mean, who wants to open
up that can of worms?
[EREN]
Okay. Who're you again?
Uh, Jean Kirschtein!
Y'know, the guy who ran
with you to school?!
Your name's Eren Jaeger?
I'm gonna go out
on a limb and say
you were the weirdo at
your last school, too.
Creep a lot of people out
with that kinda talk?
Maybe! Okay, yeah! So what?!
At my last school
I was like a rock star!
Best soccer player on the team,
high grade point average,
and I always got a ton of
cards on Valentine's day!
Sometimes a box of chocolates.
Big man, huh?
Well I may not have been
one of the popular kids,
but I had tons of fun.
I can't give specific
examples at the moment,
but trust me: it was a blast!
What's your problem?!
[BOTH growling]
[MIKASA]
Knock it off.
[JEAN gasping]
We're all in the same boat
here people, right?
It's Junior High. We need
to try and get along.
[JEAN gasping]
[MIKASA]
Something wrong?
Oh! I'm sorry, I...
You have really
beautiful black hair.
[MIKASA]
Eren! Your collar's unbuttoned!
[EREN yelps]
Back off!
Quit treating me like a toddler
you always gotta
swoop down and save!
[JEAN growls]
Bastards like you
make me wanna puke!
What the--?!
Hey, man, I don't know
who you think you are,
but rip my uniform and
you'll wish you hadn't!
[JEAN, EREN groaning]
[EREN]
Ow.
[KEITH]
Mm?
You there. Girl.
What in blazes d'you
think you're doing?
You're officially
on my bad side!
I suggest you give
me a name now!
My name is Sasha Braus, sir!
Wall Rose South Elementary!
[KEITH]
Well then, Sasha Braus.
Suppose you tell me
what you've got there
in your right hand?
Rice ball, sir!
There's a fresh,
wild-caught salmon belly
in the center and
it's delicious.
I'll bet.
Why of all places would you
choose to stuff your face here?
Well, I was going to
eat a watermelon,
but it got ruined on the way to
school, so I had to make do.
Why here? Why this moment?
Why eat that rice
ball in my class?
Uh. Are you asking my why
people eat rice balls, sir,
or are you asking me
why I didn't go
with a different kind like
spicy mayo barbeque beef?
[ALL]
Uh...
Yum.
Here, sir. You can have half.
Half. Really?
[ANNOUNCEMENT A]
Attention.
The Entrance Ceremony
will begin shortly.
All students report to the
schoolyard with their lunches.
I repeat,
all students report to the
schoolyard with their lunches.
The Entrance Ceremony
will begin shortly...
[SASHA]
With our lunches?
Fall in!
[STUDENTS]
Sir!
[KEITH]
All right.
Attack Junior High's 104th
Entrance Ceremony begins now!
First off, we'll have words
from the Head Master!
[STUDENTS gasping]
What's with the shaking?
What in the hell is that?!
[EREN gasps]
[SASHA]
Uh, oh.
No! That's impossible!
The wall's 50 meters high!
[EREN]
Oh god.
It's a titan!
And I recognize him!
No!
[EREN] He took something
precious away from me!
Eren, no! Don't tell them!
[STUDENTS screaming]
[JEAN]
Ow!
[STUDENTS screaming]
[STUDENTS]
Titans!
Eren, c'mon! We've got
to get moving!
[THOMAS screams]
[gasps]
[THOMAS whimpering]
Help me.
[SAMUEL, MILIEUS gasp]
Thomas!
[THOMAS cries]
Wait! No! My gyoza!
[MINA]
My tuna sandwich!
You bastards.
So this is how things
are gonna be.
Eren!
[SASHA]
Please, not my omelet!
[CONNY]
My mom made that fried chicken!
You've gotta snap out of it!
[EREN]
It's happening again.
They take away what
we hold most dear.
I will not be bullied!
[screams] The target's
in front of me!
[MIKASA]
Eren, wait!
[EREN] We've got ourselves
a Colossal Titan!
[HANNES]
Huh?
[EREN growls]
[EREN]
This is my chance!
Eren!
[EREN]
For us Junior High School kids,
this will be our
greatest leap ever!
[EREN yells]
[EREN yelling]
Yes! Go get him, Eren!
[EREN grunts]
[STUDENTS cheer]
Say goodbye!
[EREN]
Uh, oh.
[EREN screams]
[ALL groan]
[EREN]
Ah?! No!
Don't do it, you monster!
Not my precious
Cheese Hamburg steak!
[ALL groan]
[SASHA]
Cheese Hamburg steak?
[CHRISTA] He put his life
on the line for that?
[YMIR] Way to have your
priorities straight.
[JEAN]
That Chee-burg bastard.
[sighs] I tried to tell
not to say it out loud.
It's my... favorite.
[grunts] Yeah. Chee-burg
bastard.
[ARMIN]
Armin hates the cold.
In fact, Armin hates
the cold so much
he flat-out refuses
to go to school.
Eren and the others try
to reason with him,
but when they
get to his house,
they come face-to-face with
the strongest man in the world.