[HANNA]
We get to watch a DVD today!
[FRANZ]
Fun!
That's kinda weird.
Whoever sits at that
desk never shows up.
Huh? Oh, Armin.
Poor guy really hates the cold,
so during the Winter
he just stays home.
But it's already Spring.
How warm's it gotta be for
him to come to school?
He needs to start thinking
about his attendance record.
I wonder if he's okay.
Let's drop by and check
on him after class.
[KEITH]
What's going on here?!
[EREN]
Mr. Keith!
[KEITH] Care to explain
why you kids are the only
students who haven't
signed up for a club yet?!
Oh. Right.
Sir, is there a club dedicated
to beating up Titans?
'Cause I would join
that in a heartbeat.
Well, that was certainly
an Eren response.
[KEITH]
Eren Jaeger!
Sir!
You and the absentee
Armin Arlett
went to the same elementary
school, correct?
[EREN]
Uh. Yes, sir!
[KEITH]
Good.
I expect you to collect his club
submission form by tomorrow.
If you fail, I'll put him
and the whole lot of you
in whatever club I
damn well feel like.
Is that clear?
[EREN whimpers]
[STORE CLERK A]
Thank you. Come again.
[EREN]
Meat buns and amazake.
If a grab-bag of these
doesn't get him out of
the house, nothin' will.
[doorbell rings]
[EREN]
Hello?
[MIKASA, EREN gasp]
[EREN gasps]
He took the meat buns!
You monster!
[MIKASA]
Eren, wait!
[EREN]
Give them back right now!
They don't belong to you!
Ugh! Let go of me
you filthy Titan!
Or taste my iron fist!
At this rate the meat buns
are gonna get cold.
[EREN screams]
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[EREN grunts]
Who is that?
[EREN]
Mm?
[MAN grunts]
Look at that emblem.
The wings... of freedom.
And that uniform.
He's definitely
an upperclassman.
[EREN]
Huh?
Hey. You two.
This is the part where you
tell me what's going on.
[EREN]
That does it.
I'm joining whatever
club this guy's in.
Don't you see?
That's how I'll hone my
Titan-fighting skills!
Then I'm gonna join it, too.
[EREN] Uh?! What?
No way, forget about it!
I'm not tryin' to drag you in.
Don't follow me to my doom!
No. But if I can help it,
with me there, it
won't be your doom.
Together then.
'Scuse me.
Still kinda still waitin'
on an explanation here.
Uh, sir?
Mind if I ask what
club you belong to?
Its unofficial name is
"None of Your Damn
Business, Chee-burg."
[EREN]
Huh?
[ARMIN'S GRANDPA]
Cleaning the futon,
the filthy, filthy futon.
Ha! Ha! Ha!
That's Armin's grandfather.
[LEVI growls] Hey, pops. That's
not how you clean a futon!
Quit flinging the
beater like a whip.
You'll damage the batting!
Use a sideways motion!
[ARMIN'S GRANDPA] Whoa!
What're you doing?
[EREN]
Uh...
[LEVI]
Give it here!
I'll show you how
to do it properly!
We ought'a go see
if Armin's home.
[EREN]
Armin. It's us.
[MIKASA]
We have stuff for you. Open up.
[ARMIN]
I can't!
[MIKASA, EREN]
Huh?
If I step outside, this
hellish cold will end me.
My constitution is too delicate.
C'mon, man. Winter's over.
[ARMIN]
No. You're wrong.
Winter never ends.
This world is hell.
It didn't become hell,
it's been hell.
We're all condemned.
I just wasn't able
to see it before.
We're caught between
a Siberian cold front
and a low-pressure system.
I think he's lost his marbles.
Armin, please. Come out.
We've got a bag of
meat buns and amazake.
Seriously?!
Ah. It's so nice and warm!
[MIKASA, EREN groan]
Armin, are you okay?
You're not burning up?
I'm good.
[MIKASA sighs]
Mikasa, if the heat's
bothering you that much,
just take your
scarf off already.
Uh. I'm fine. I just need
to open up a window
or something so we can get
some fresh air in here.
Please don't.
The cold goes right through me
even when I'm
wrapped in my futon.
Not hard to tell why.
That thing's definitely
seen better days.
[ARMIN]
Huh? Oh, no!
[EREN] It's not a big deal.
Just buy a new one.
Impossible!
Me and my futon have been thick
as thieves since I was a child.
It's part of me. Like an
old, trusted friend.
I'm sorry. It's irreplaceable.
[EREN]
Uh! It's you!
[ARMIN] What's happening?
What's going on?
Tch. Give me that thing.
My futon!
We can't let him get away!
[MIKASA]
Right behind you.
[ARMIN]
Wait for me!
Anyone see which way he went?
[ARMIN]
Why?
[EREN]
Mm?
[ARMIN] That futon was my
most prized possession.
Cold days or cool, it cradled
me in its delicious warmth.
What will I ever do without it?
[sneezes]
This ought'a pull you through
till we get it back.
You're a good friend.
We know who's got it.
Question is how do
we track him down?
[MIKASA]
Eren, look at this.
[EREN] Whoa! That's the pin
from the back of his jacket!
We should show it around school.
Somebody's bound
to know something.
You're a genius! Let's go!
Yay! A clue! [sneezes]
[EREN gasps]
[EREN]
What's up with you guys?!
Don't tell me there was
another Titan attack!
[SASHA] I thought if I
joined the Cooking Club
I'd be able to eat
whenever I want.
You stuffed your face with all
the ingredients, didn't you?
I got recruited to
the baseball club
on account of my
close-cropped hair, but--
How do they expect you
to swing that bat?
I scoped out the soccer club
and it was a disaster.
They ought to call it pushball
so you know what you'll
be getting' into.
[sighs] I don't know
what's going on
with this school,
but I'm not a fan.
[REINER] All the clubs
are like that here.
[JEAN]
Hu? Reiner.
The Judo Club's a total joke.
And Ymir says the same
thing about Band.
Titans basically run the show.
[JEAN grunts]
[ARMIN sneezes]
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[ARMIN]
Mm...
[CHRISTA]
So... who's he?
Oh. This is Armin.
Our buddy who's been
absent from school.
Uh, nice to meet you a--
[sneezes]
Uh, is he okay?
That's one heck of
a sneeze attack.
Hey, are you contagious?
Don't worry, he's just
susceptible to colds
when he's not wrapped
up in his futon.
That reminds me.
Have any of you
seen this before?
We're lookin' for
the guy it belongs to.
He ran off with Armin's futon
after takin' out a
Titan in one blow.
Someone took out a Titan?
Yeah, sure. Whatever, man.
No. Wait.
I've heard about this.
Word through the grapevine is
there's a secret organization
on campus that rebels
against the Titans.
Their symbol is the
Wings of Freedom.
So you're tellin' me
there is a club where
you beat up Titans!
Wow. He looks happy.
Guys. I have feeling that's
where my futon is.
There's more to it
than that. A lot more.
Rumor has it the strongest man
in the world is a member.
The world? That's really strong.
I like me the sound of that.
Ha! My kinda club!
You think if we join they'll
teach how to fight
so we can actually keep our
lunches safe for a change?
Taking down a Titan's gotta
be worth serious points
with the hotties in this school.
[EREN] What's the club's name?
I have to sign up!
[REINER]
Easy there, champ.
Like I said, it's a
secret organization.
It's not like they'll have
a sign over their door.
[EREN]
"Attack Junior Scout Regiment."
[CHRISTA] That was easier
than I thought it would be.
[REINER] Yeah, well, I was just
going by what I heard, okay?
[YMIR] Do secret organizations
usually advertise?
It's like a clubhouse
for a bunch of
elementary school brats.
Honestly, I'm starting to
get a little discouraged.
What's wrong with you
guys? Knock it off!
The strongest man
might be in there!
You wanna talk smack
about his club
where there's a good
chance he'll hear us?
[ORUO]
Will you kids shut up?
[EREN gasping]
Why are you here?
If you're laboring under
the misguided assumption
we're a secret,
below-board organization
dedicated to standing up
against the Titan scourge,
you've wasted your time.
[EREN]
So it's true!
No.
There must've been
some kind of mistake.
The very existence of the Scout
Regiment is shrouded in secrecy.
There's no way a bunch of First
Year dolts have heard of us.
You're pretty much
giving it all away.
No kidding. Wow.
[EREN]
Let us in! Please!
[BOTH grunting]
We're just looking for our
buddy's futon, all right?
We don't want to
cause any trouble.
You have a lot of nerve!
What makes you think
we're in the habit
of submitting to the
demands of whoever
decides to
show up at our door--
[ORUO groaning]
[PETRA, ELD, GUNTER gasp]
Oruo!
[GUNTER]
Who did this, an assassin?
[ELD]
Unbelievable.
What kind of animal
cuts a man's tongue?!
The faculty's marked
us for death!
[EREN]
Excuse me.
[ELD, PETRA, GUNTER]
Hm?
He, uh... He bit his tongue
when he smacked himself
with the door, I think.
[ORUO groaning]
That checks out.
Oruo bites his tongue on average
about three times a day.
I'm waiting for when he has
the decency to bleed out.
Hey! That was not a
nice thing to say!
I bit my tongue because
these clowns showed up
and demanded to be let in!
[PETRA] What can you do?
They're First Years.
[ORUO]
Hmph!
We are shadowy organization
that operates in secret.
I don't suppose we can expect
First Year know-nothings
to make an appointment, can we?
Granted, the "futon"
gambit was...
Hi, I'm Petra.
Nice to meet you guys.
So is it true?
You really wanna join the Attack
Junior High Scout Regiment?
Yes!
Oh, 'least that part
of why we're here.
We were also hoping to find the
guy who wears this pendant.
[footsteps]
[EREN, JEAN yelp]
Hi, Hange!
[GUNTER]
It's Miche! Welcome back!
Hey guys. Guess what I found?
A fresh supply of Titan
fingernail clippings:
direct from the dumpster
to your keepsake shelf!
That's funny.
There're a lot of faces
here I don't recognize.
[PETRA]
They're First Years.
They came by to check
us out. Maybe even join!
[HANGE]
Really? There's so many of them!
Who'd have thought we'd
get this much interest?!
Ah, ha, ha, ha!
That's so cool!
I bet you young
'uns want to join
because you're super
into stuff like this!
Not really, no.
There's no need to
hide how you feel!
If you want to dismember Titans,
all in the name of better
understanding them, of course.
This is most definitely
the place you want to be!
Hange! You'll scare them off!
[EREN]
What is the deal with this club?
I feel like we've stumbled
into a nest of psychos.
[CONNY]
Ah!
Still, though.
When you get right down to it,
these people want change.
There's a reason they call
themselves the Scout Regiment.
Uh, excuse me,
but we're looking for the
person who took my futon--
Futon? Oh, yeah. I saw
Levi walking around
with one a little
while ago, actually.
[MICHE grunts]
That's the guy! Yeah!
D'you know where he is?
If that's what you're
interested in, here.
What am I supposed
to do with this?
[HANGE]
Go on! Do it!
Uh. Okay.
Eren!
[ARMIN whimpers]
Hey. Moron.
Recyclables go
in a separate bin.
You don't just throw
plastic in the trash.
Hello, Levi!
Excellent form on
the slap, as usual.
Then again, you are the
strongest man in the world!
[LEVI]
Can it, Abnormal.
[EREN]
I knew it had to be true.
He is the strongest
man in the world!
Hey, that's my futon he's got!
Why did you... [sneezes]
Why'd you take it?
[sneezing]
[LEVI]
Isn't it obvious?
Huh?
Since when does a
man need excuses
to repair a damaged futon?
--[MIKASA growling]
--[ARMIN sneezes]
[ARMIN]
Ah!
You made him stop sneezing!
He's without it for five minutes
and he catches a cold?
I'd say somebody needs to
get himself in better shape.
Ah. It hasn't been
this warm in years!
Maybe if he wears that thing
he'll actually start
showing up to class.
That's a good idea!
Way to go, Armin, good for you!
Aw, you guys! Thank you!
[EREN]
Levi!
[ALL]
Huh?
Please let me join the Attack
Junior High Scout Regiment!
Easy there, Chee-burg.
This place is a sty.
[EREN]
Huh?
[LEVI] Get to cleaning
and I'll consider it.
So, then,
you really think you have
what it takes to be a Scout?
Yes! Please let me sign up, sir!
[LEVI] I need to know
that you fully understand
the risks involved.
If the school finds out,
you'll be expelled.
As in kicked out, for good.
Are you prepared for that?
Yeah! We were born
prepared, sir!
Hell yeah!
We care a lot more about
lunch than our transcripts!
I want my mom's
fried chicken back!
What about you, Chee-burg?
What's in this for you?
It's an easy question, for most.
What is it you want to do?
For me?
I want to join the Scouts,
and slaughter every Titan
that crosses my path!
[LEVI] Well played.
Good enough for me.
[ALL scream]
[EREN groaning]
What are you doin'?
Uh?
[EREN]
Whoa!
Good news, First Years.
You're all now officially
members of the Scouts.
This is gonna be epic!
Hooray shadowy organization!
Ha! This is great!
Now the Wings of Freedom
belong to us all!
What about our other clubs?
We ought to be able
to switch, right?
I mean, we've still
got some time.
[EREN] Wait, Wall Cleanup?!
What the hell?!
We turned in our submission
forms on time!
The Scout Regiment
is unauthorized.
Don't tell me you
thought the school
would approve your membership?
--[ALL gasping]
--[HANGE laughs]
--[LEVI] Idiots.
[ALL]
No!
[MIKASA sighs]
[ARMIN]
"I will crush you."
Thirsty for revenge,
Annie challenges Eren to a
cutthroat game of dodge-ball.
When all is said and done,
the source of her burning hatred
will become all too clear.