[BERTHOLDT]
All done!
Whoa. Wow, Bertholdt!
That's pretty neat!
It's amazing.
It's not that big of a deal.
Just the one thing I'm good at.
[REINER]
Bertholdt.
Bertholdt!
How does he sleep like that?
Hey, good for him.
I don't get why's he gotta be
all artsy about it, though.
[CONNY] I think it means the
sun'll come out tomorrow?
Bertholdt! Wake the hell up!
Uh. Sorry.
Okay, that stung a little bit.
Mornin', Reiner. How's it goin'?
[REINER] Fine. Listen,
I've got a favor to ask.
Oh, yeah?
It's... It's important.
[BERTHOLDT]
Mm?
Look, I need your help.
I was thinking about asking
Christa to the Summer Festival.
[BERTHOLDT]
Uh?!
[yawns] That's nice. Good luck.
[REINER] You're coming along
for the ride! I need a wingman!
What d'you mean?
I'd just be third wheel,
it'll cramp your style.
Look, in an ideal world
of course I'd want the girl
all to myself. Thing is...
Go on.
I'm... too... embarrassed.
Oh.
I bare my soul to you and
that's all you have to say?
[REINER]
Smirk.
Yeah. Just to be clear, I need
this to be a double date.
Wait. I gotta ask someone out?
Who?
Annie seems like a good choice.
Don't be ridiculous! Why
would I go out with Annie?
Talk about outta left field!
It's not like I harbor
secret feelings...
[REINER]
The guy's an open book.
You know what'd be great?
You and me stopping at the crepe
place over by your house!
Sure. You'll get fat.
Oh, god! Do I look like
I'm gaining weight?!
[REINER]
Got a minute, Christa?
I was wondering if
you'd like to go
to the Summer Festival with
me on Saturday, or whatever.
I mean. If you want.
I'd love to!
[REINER]
Seriously?!
[YMIR]
What the hell?!
The festival was supposed
to be a you-and-me thing!
Don't be silly! It's more
fun if we all go together!
[YMIR growls]
Who else d'you think
we should ask along?
[YMIR] Hey! Don't just
stand there like an idiot!
Say something
[REINER]
Mm?
I vote we make it
a big group! Party!
Hm... Oh, yeah! And I'll bet
they have a crepe stall!
I am totally going
to stuff my face!
[REINER, YMIR]
Smirk.
Here's the deal, Berthie.
I'm pretty much gonna shadow
Christa the entire time
so she doesn't get mauled
by a gorilla or something.
A gorilla?
I'm not up for grabs
in this scenario.
Best bet is to ask Annie.
Don't be ridiculous!
Why would I do that?
Talk about outta left field!
[YMIR, REINER]
Worst poker face ever.
Hey, Annie. Got a minute?
Bertholdt has a question
he'd like to ask you.
[BERTHOLDT gasps]
Reiner! Ugh! Seriously?
Now?! Right now?!
Yes! Do not wuss out!
This is your chance!
[ANNIE]
What's up?
[BERTHOLDT]
U-Um, uh.
[ANNIE]
Hm?
[BERTHOLDT]
Uh, uh... D'you.
maybe...
wanna... Uh!
come with all of us to the
Summer Festival this Saturday?!
The Summer Festival?
Nah, no thanks.
Not really my scene.
[EREN]
Oooo! I wanna go!
Sounds like it'd be a blast!
Wherever Eren goes, I go.
Ooo. Festival! I'm in!
Yakisoba, cotton
candy, shaved ice,
grilled squid,
octopus dumplings!
Cool! Think they'll
have fried chicken?
Heh. Stick with me and
I'll teach you yokels
how to enjoy the Summer
Festival like a boss.
All right! This will
be so much fun!
See? D'aw! You're gonna love it!
[ANNIE]
What? I wasn't planning...
[REINER, YMIR, BERTHOLDT]
Wow. That escalated quickly.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
We've got some stragglers now.
But look on the bright side:
you did technically ask her out.
I guess. Sort of.
C'mon, get off it.
Look, what's done is done, okay?
It's time for you to man up.
The festival's a
golden opportunity.
Tell her the truth,
she's not gonna bite.
Uh. Uh... Truth about what?
[REINER] Nice try. We all see
the way you look at her.
[BERTHOLDT gasps]
Really hope you weren't
trying to be sneaky,
'cause it's painfully obvious.
[BERTHOLDT]
Huh?
[YMIR]
We should call you Stare-tholdt.
[BERTHOLDT screams]
Don't come apart on me, dude.
Accept and move on.
This is your chance to tell her
how you really feel. Take it.
Don't be an idiot.
How's he supposed
to spill the beans
with the jackass brigade in tow?
If he doesn't come
clean now, he never will.
And it's not like we have the
option of uninviting everyone.
[YMIR] Duh, I know. Guess
your boy's up a creek.
Sorry.
[REINER]
Nah. No worries.
I've got a plan.
[YMIR]
Uh, oh. Is it stupid?
[BERTHOLDT]
How did this happen?
All I want is to be with Annie.
[REINER] Look at me.
Stick to the plan and we'll
lock this down, got it?
[BERTHOLDT]
Yeah, sure.
Moving into phase one.
First, tell her
she looks adorable!
[REINER (BERTHOLDT)]
Wow, Annie.
Love the candy coating.
You look adorable.
[REINER (ANNIE)]
Oh, Bertholdt. Kiss!
[REINER] The key is to
focus on something specific.
Right.
[CHRISTA]
Thanks for waiting!
[BERTHOLDT]
Hm?
I'm sorry.
Took me longer than I
thought to get dressed.
[REINER]
She's... so cute!
Totally all right!
We haven't been here long!
Hey! Like the look! It's
absolutely adorable--
Yeah, that yukata is
absolutely adorable on you.
Hey, wanna get married
after the festival's over?
Heh. You're sweet.
[REINER growls]
Oh, Annie looks pretty swank,
too, wouldn't say, Bertie?
Oh, uh, oh, I-uh!
[YMIR]
We're waiting!
Oh, uh! You, you look, uh...
I'll give you a little hint:
it has to do with her yukata.
You. Uh, I mean. Annie.
[YMIR, REINER]
Now! Say it!
I'm really liking that knot
you have on your geta strap.
[REINER, YMIR]
Ow. Damn it!
That's too specific.
[EREN]
Hey, guys!
Was this where we were
supposed to meet up?
[SASHA gasps] Oh, wow! You're
rockin' that yukata, Annie!
It was a present from my dad.
Oh, Hey, guys. What'cha
got goin' on down there?
[YMIR, REINER growl]
Whaddya think we
oughta do first?
Meh. I dunno.
Just be sure to not blow through
this month's allowance,
your mom asked me to remind you.
I'm craving octopus dumplings!
[SASHA] I love a yukata
on you, too, Christa!
[CHRISTA]
How come you're not wearing one?
[SASHA]
I went jinbei.
A yukata's too tight
around the tummy.
[REINER]
Fine! On to phase two!
Show her your manly side...
at the shooting gallery!
I'm tellin' you, there's
nothing more macho
at a festival than a
sharpshooter stall.
This booth looks kinda
cool, wanna give it a try?
Sure. I'm game.
Uh? Hey kiddos!
The name's Ness.
I'm the proprietor
of this stall.
This here's my pet
hamster, Charrette.
She has sort of a thing
for chewing on folks' hair,
so be careful 'less you
figure on goin' bald--
[groaning]
You do know what they
say about a man
who can deadeye his target.
He can put an arrow straight
through the heart
of his ladylove.
[REINER (BERTHOLDT)]
Here you go, Annie.
I won it. Just for you.
[REINER (ANNIE)]
Oh, Bertholdt! Kiss!
[BERTHOLDT]
Whoa.
[CONNY]
Check out that aim!
Mikasa just bagged the
biggest prize in the booth
on her first shot!
[SASHA gasps]
[EREN growling]
[MIKASA]
Eren. This is for you.
Uh. Sorry, what's goin' on?
You, looked hungry.
Pork Fillet Cutlet-hungry.
[EREN]
What kind of look is that?!
No way! Another
on the first try!
Hey. so, uh...
if no one's gonna
eat that, maybe...
[BOTH]
Mister, one more time, please.
[NESS] Could you not run me
out of business, please?
[REINER, BERTHOLDT] Well, this
clearly wasn't the way to go.
Don't worry, my plan
still has a trump card
that'll completely
turn this around!
Trust me, it's foolproof!
Anyone else hot?
I could go for some
shaved ice right now.
Yeah, good idea.
Want some, Annie?
Guess that sounds okay--
Sounds brilliant!
Tell you what: let me buy some
for everybody, my treat!
I'll help carry!
[REINER]
No, wait! Guys!
Ugh. Fine!
It shouldn't affect the outcome.
Moving to Phase Three.
Operation "Look out, your
yukata'll get stained!"
First, Ymir will hand
Annie her shaved ice.
[REINER (YMIR)]
Uh-oh!
[REINER] Just when it's
about to plop smack-dab
on her nice outfit, sploosh!
[REINER (BERTHOLDT)]
You okay? Sorry 'bout that.
[REINER (ANNIE)]
It's all right.
I'd prefer a chocolate-coated
banana anyway.
Ahh. Love-love-love!
[REINER] What'd I tell ya?
It's your ace in the hole!
Uh... just...
Huh. Sure is taking them
a long time to get back.
[REINER]
I think we left the wrong people
in charge of reconnaissance.
I wouldn't be surprised
if they got lost.
[MAN A]
My pleasure, miss!
[BERTHOLDT]
Annie?
Damn! Phase Three's
a bust at this rate!
So? Just tweak your
stupid plan already.
[BERTHOLDT] Or, we could
just forget about it.
Oh. Great. And now
he's backing out.
What?! Dude! We're
trying to help!
Look, I know you mean well.
But seriously, putting Annie
in this position isn't cool.
[CONNY]
We made it back!
Huh. See?
That's what we get for taking
one of your shortcuts.
Where were you?
Don't worry about it,
enjoy your shaved ice!
[JEAN] It's basically
flavored water now!
[SASHA] If you don't want it,
I'll take it!
[JEAN]
Hands off!
[YMIR]
Smirk.
[JEAN grunting]
[YMIR]
Uh, oh!
Annie! Look out!
[ALL gasping]
[CHRISTA, ANNIE whimper]
[gasps]
[ANNIE]
Bertholdt.
You okay? Nothing
on your clothes?
[ANNIE]
N-No, I'm fine.
Good.
Nice save! Good thing
Bertholdt was around, huh?
Yeah! I'll say!
Those were some
catlike reflexes!
Are you okay?
You got drenched.
[BERTHOLDT] No worries,
I'll just go wash up.
Excuse me. I'm gonna
need a minute.
Uh, sure thing.
[BERTHOLDT sighs]
Look at me.
All this BS. 'Cause I don't
know how to talk to her.
[BOSS A]
Come one, come all!
Step right up and enjoy
some first-rate die-cutting!
You find him?
[JEAN]
He wasn't by the restrooms.
[SASHA] Where did he go? I
thought that he was coming back.
Crap. He totally freaked out.
We got too carried away.
He's gotta be somewhere.
I say we scatter.
[YMIR grunts]
[BERTHOLDT]
Uh? All done.
[BOSS A] Nice job.
Can that be it for now?
C'mon, kid. I'm a workin' man.
You keep this pace up, you're
gonna drive me outta business.
How 'bout some bonus prizes?
Both of 'em?
[BOSS A] Yeah, why not? One for
you, one for your girlfriend.
[BERTHOLDT] Oh! My what?
She's not my girlfriend!
[ANNIE] This is where
we all agreed to meet
once somebody found you.
The others oughta be here soon.
[BERTHOLDT] Sorry. You
must've looked everywhere.
[ANNIE]
Not really.
I knew you were a big
fan of die-cutting.
[BERTHOLDT gasps]
You remembered that, huh?
[ANNIE]
Of course I did.
So I had fairly good idea
where you might be.
[BERTHOLDT]
Makes sense.
I can't remember the last time
I'd been to a summer
festival, though.
Sorry. I shouldn't
have asked you.
I know it's not your scene,
but I hope you're
having a little fun.
It's not terrible.
I just hate crowds.
[gasps] I'm sorry!
[ANNIE]
Don't be.
Honestly, getting me out here
was probably a good thing.
[BERTHOLDT]
Huh?
[ANNIE] Because it's with you,
I mean. Don't take that weird.
I just don't do well around,
you know, people. And you.
You're someone I can
be myself with.
Mainly... because I don't
have to make small talk.
Does that put me in the Friend
Zone or somewhere even worse?
[ANNIE] Really, I think
of you like... like air.
[BERTHOLDT]
That's way worse!
[ANNIE laughs]
[BERTHOLDT gasps]
[ANNIE laughing]
[gasps] Hey, guys! Over here!
[YMIR]
Shh! Shut. up.
[ANNIE laughing]
Sorry, that was mean.
--[BERTHOLDT] Annie, would--
--[ANNIE] I shouldn't--
[gasps]
Annie. How do I say
this? Would you...?
[inaudible]
Sure.
[gasps]
Yes!
[ALL groaning]
[CHRISTA]
Uh...
What're you doing?
[REINER laughs] You did it,
man! I'm proud of ya!
[YMIR] I knew you'd work
around to it eventually.
It was only a matter of time.
Aw, thanks. It's no big deal.
Hey! Why don't we all
do some die-cutting!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[YMIR, REINER sigh]
Fantastic. All that trouble and
she said yes to die-cutting.
The perfect moment was
staring him in the face.
[EREN yells]
It keeps breaking!
You're good at this, Bertholdt.
Wow, look at that!
Thanks. It takes patience,
the secret's not to rush things.
See, if you're in a hurry,
you always press too hard
and wind up damaging it,
especially if you're
not super careful...
[REINER]
It's a start.
[BERTHOLDT gasps]
[CONNY]
Whoa! Awesome!
They're beautiful!
Wow! Incredible!
Beautiful.
[BERTHOLDT]
Huh?
They certainly are.
[ARMIN]
Student council elections.
The goal is to be president.
Many are the ambitious
souls who run.
Legend tells of a
mysterious notebook
whose content heavily influences
the electoral outcome.