Right! Today's the day!
Yakisoba bread,
you're mine!
Ah!
Uh?! [screams]
Thank you Levi, darling!
I'll pay you back today
before yesterday!
[LEVI]
Like hell, Four Eyes!
Come back, yakisoba!
You and me belong together!
[SASHA sniffs] Life is cruel.
Once again, no yakisoba.
It's so unfair!
Yeah, that's a real tragedy.
You do know there's an unspoken
rule banning First Years
from buying bread in
the cafeteria, right?
The upperclassmen must have a
serious thing for baked goods.
Ugh. Not the point.
They just like to rub our
noses in their superiority.
Whoa! That's not very nice!
[EREN]
On the subject, what's with you
ditching Wall Cleanup
Club lately?
[JEAN whistles]
If I was you, I'd make it
a point to show up today.
Rico's super ticked.
[EREN]
Hey there, Rico!
How's it goin' this afternoon?
Not bad. Long time
no see, Jean.
Mind telling me why you've been
skipping out on cleanup duties?
Uh, yeah, well,
I've been crazy busy
with afterschool dance
class and karate.
I know for a fact none
of that is true.
Bad enough your turned you
back on the sacred trust
that is Wall Cleanup duty,
but to stand there
and lie to me!
Forgiveness is not an option,
and as far as I'm concerned,
you're all responsible
for Jean's misconduct,
so you're on window detail!
[ALL]
What!
[CONNY sighs]
I'm exhausted.
[SASHA]
I'm on the verge of starvation.
[EREN]
Hey. Sorry we're late. We got--
[ORUO]
Unacceptable!
You must utter an
appropriate greeting!
Oh, uh, good afternoon, then.
I can't hear you!
[ALL]
Uh! Good afternoon!
Why do I get the feeling
you've been slacking off?
You've been remiss in your
commitments, haven't you, runt?
Don't even think
about lying to me!
I wouldn't dream of it!
Explain the state of your dress!
You look like you
just got out of bed!
I expect to see you in
uniform at all times!
And heaven help you if the
collar's left unbuttoned!
First Years are not allowed
to trick out their bags
with adorable keychains!
I'm sorry! I didn't know!
What's this crap, son?
You tryin' to
impress the ladies?
Colored tee-shirts
are forbidden!
Whoa! Violation!
Skirt hemlines go
below the knee!
And absolutely no cute
needlepoint designs
on your socks!
Aw, seriously?
Somebody needs
a haircut, stat!
Turn around, girlie-boy!
First Years get a One Guard!
--[ARMIN] No!
--[CONNY] That's what I use! Ha!
[ELD] Zip up that tracksuit!
All the way!
[PETRA]
First Year females must
tie their hair back
above the ear!
[GUNTHER] Come to school
in designer shoes,
and you'll answer to us!
[ORUO] It's within regulations
for me to backhand you!
Can everybody shut
up for a second?!
[ALL gasp]
[ORUO groaning]
[CHRISTA]
Hi guys! What' up?
Oh, I mean "good afternoon,"
sorry we're late.
[UPPERCLASSMEN gasping]
[UPPERCLASSMEN]
Unacceptable!
[EREN sighs]
[JEAN] This sucks. We're stuck
cleaning wherever we go.
[EREN]
I know.
It feels like we'll be doing
this for the rest of our lives.
[ARMIN]
Oh, now. It's not that bad.
Junior High's only three
years, after all.
I'll catch you!
[YMIR grunts]
You all right, love?
Thank you so much, Ymir!
When this cleaning is done,
you and me are getting married.
[HANGE]
How's it going in here?
[EREN]
Hange! Levi!
[HANGE]
I don't know why,
but for some reason
this all seems familiar.
Morons. How long have
you been at this?
Uh. I don't know,
maybe something like
ten minutes or so?
You are beyond pathetic.
The three of us could get
it cleaner in two minutes.
How are you gonna be equal
to your Scout duties
when you can't even
dust a store room?
But we've been...
We've been working as
hard as we can, sir!
[JEAN] Yap, yap clean yap.
What are you two, in-laws?
Yeah, this is dumb!
"Man cannot live by bread
alone," said some guy.
And why can't I by me
some yakisoba bread?!
And how come everybody isn't
required to use a One Guard?
Hey, calm down!
We'll get in trouble!
[ALL gasping]
[LEVI] What you need is
to be taught a lesson.
And you're in perfect kicking
position, says this guy.
I say we need a friendly
competition!
And that it's important for
all of us to be involved!
So, let's set an example
for the First Years!
[PETRA] Huh? Uh.
Don't drag us into this!
Ugh, damn it! Why me?
[LEVI]
Done deal.
Whoever loses cleans
the Titan building.
[ALL gasping]
[LEVI]
It's on, day after tomorrow.
Against each other and everyone
else in the Sports Day Games.
[ILSE]
Hello and welcome to the annual
Attack Junior High
Sports Day Games!
I'm your commentator,
Ilse Lagnar with the Newspaper
Club, comin' at you live!
Aw, jeez. I don't get it,
how in the world'd we
let this happen to us?
[CHRISTA]
You guys!
[ALL]
Huh?
[CHRISTA] Sorry I'm late!
Took me a while to change!
[YMIR, REINER]
She's so cute!
[ANNIE]
Um, Christa.
[CHRISTA]
Uh?
I'm really not
feeling this outfit.
Don't be that way! It's normal
to feel self-conscious.
You'll get over it!
[ANNIE]
Look. I'm tellin' you.
I can hardly breathe
in this damn thing.
[BERTHOLDT moaning]
Okay, everyone!
Get out there and win
it for the First Years!
Yeah! Let's give it
everything we've got!
[ALL]
Yeah!
We got this in the bag!
[ANNIE]
Sure.
[CHRISTA]
Uh-huh!
[ILSE]
All right, folks!
Those participating in
the bun-eating contest,
report to the area near the
entrance gate at this time!
It's my turn now and
momma's gonna win!
[EREN]
Good luck, Sasha!
Like I need luck for this one!
[MIKASA]
Uh...? Uh...
[SASHA] Red bean paste,
yakisoba, melon.
How long I've waited to stuff
myself with your deliciousness!
[HANGE] Hello, Sasha! Here's
hopin' we both do okay!
Ho-ho, trust me. I'll do fine!
[HANNES] Okay! Let the eating
competition begin!
Everybody on their marks.
Set.
[SASHA yells]
Come on, Sasha! Woo!
Hold up. What's going on?
Is Hange
not even gonna try?
[SASHA] What did I just
tell ya? This one's mine!
Hey! No way that's regulation!
Why not?
We're basically two halves
of the same person!
[SASHA growls]
[HANGE laughs]
Good one, Sawney!
You almost got me there!
[MOBLIT] One of these day's it's
gonna be a lot more than almost!
Can't I have even a tiny piece?
Sasha. Fight on!
[ANNIE]
Yeah. What she said.
[REINER moans]
[ILSE] Next up, it's First
Years versus Second Years
in Ball Toss!
[RICO grunts]
[ILSE]
Both teams, ready.
Set.
I'm holding up my end.
Now, if Ian and the others
land some points.
[gasps]
Hey, no fair,
he's playin' dirty!
Wanna do somethin' about it,
stop whining and get up here!
[STUDENTS yelling]
[RICO] This is not what our
precious ODM gear is meant for!
[CONNY grunts]
There's our opening!
[RICO] How dare you take
Wall Cleanup Club property
without permission?
[JEAN screams]
Ow, ow.
Oh. Hi there.
Nice morning for a game, heh.
Do it.
[JEAN groaning]
Wow. The Second Years are scary.
And Jean's so
useless it's tragic.
If we put our balls in
the basket right now,
we'd probably get murdered.
[JEAN groaning]
Fight on!
[ANNIE]
Sure. That.
[REINER moans]
[ARMIN] Our team o-only
has five points.
There so much freakin' better
than us at everything,
what chance do we really have?
Well, suppose we better
just adjust to the idea
of cleaning the Titan building.
Um, maybe if we just
apologized to them?
[MIKASA]
Calm yourself.
[ALL]
Mm?
[ARMIN]
Mikasa!
[MIKASA]
We haven't got the time for you
to start getting all emotional.
Marco. Correct me
if I'm wrong,
but if we yank the bandanas off
their captains in Shoulder Wars,
we'll get a hundred points.
That about right?
Yeah. I think so.
But even with your help, there's
just way too many of them.
[MIKASA]
I can do it!
[MARCO]
What?
[MIKASA]
I'm strong. Real strong!
I am a warrior!
I can take more punishment
than any of you
and annihilate our
upperclassmen!
Even if I have to do it alone.
As far as I'm concerned,
I am surrounded by a bunch of
unskilled, cowardly worms.
You disappoint me.
You can just sit here and
twiddle your thumbs.
And watch how it's done!
'Kay, I was sorta expecting
something more motivational.
C'mon! I don't know
about you people,
but I wasn't taught to let
my comrades fight alone!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[EREN]
Mikasa! Let's make this happen!
Eren.
[ILSE]
Attention!
It's time for the last game
of the day: Shoulder Wars!
All participants report
to your designated areas!
I repeat: It's time for
the last game of the day...
Crap! We gotta hurry!
[ARMIN]
Mikasa.
Talk to you for a sec?
[ILSE] All right! We're down to
final competition:
Shoulder Wars!
The object is to
steal the bandanas
from the opposing
teams' captains.
Here we go! Everybody ready.
Set.
[ALL yelling]
[GIRL STUDENT A screams]
[BOY STUDENT A screams]
[CONNY]
Dude, Mikasa's a total badass!
How is she even goin' that fast?
Looks like this might
be a quicker game
than we thought, just remember,
we gotta get to their captains
before they get to us!
Okay!
Don't get cocky, yet!
It ain't over till
the fat la-- [groans]
That's what you get
for flapping your jowls
while carrying me on your back.
[PETRA gasps]
What?! No!
No!
You! You're in flagrant
violation of our made-up rules!
[ORUO]
Petra! Sit up straight!
[PETRA]
Huh?!
[EREN]
I'll take that!
[PETRA screams]
[EREN]
I did it!
I got a captain's bandana!
Yeah-eah!
I did it, Mikasa!
[MIKASA]
Up top!
Not bad for a noob!
Rico! Take care of the
First Years in back!
Mine and Mitabi's team will
deal with the ones out front.
Roger that!
These poor fools thought
we were scary before,
wait till they get a load
of us at full power!
C'mon, Eren! Get out there!
I'll run on ahead
and hold them off!
[EREN]
Wait! Mikasa!
[ARMIN]
You heard the girl!
Now's the time to go all in
and do whatever we can!
[EREN growls]
[MITABI]
Heads up, rugrats!
Daddy's gonna have to
spank your little bottoms
with a baseball bat!
--[ALL groaning]
--[EREN] Armin!
Go! Now!
Fulfill your duty!
[yells]
[ALL groaning]
[CONNY]
Argh! My eyes!
[SASHA]
My afternoon snack!
[HANNA] Help me, Armin!
Please! Franz is, oh no!
It's okay, Eren!
Don't look back!
Focus on the Third Year captain!
Break through!
[EREN, REINER]
Huh?
[EREN]
Levi? Wh-What're you doing?
What's it look like?
Somebody's got to
clean this mess.
You're in the way. Move it.
Don't back down!
C'mon, stay strong!
This is our big chance!
You're right! Moment of truth!
Do we falter?
Do we waste our teammates'
sacrifices?
Do we roll over and tidy up
after a bunch of Titans?
No!
Look at us!
We're still standing!
The game isn't decided yet!
Let's go!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[ALL yelling]
[LEVI gasps]
That bandana is mine!
[ALL groaning]
Watch where you're
going, idiots.
Ugh. I just swept over there.
[HANGE] Hey!
[LEVI]
Hm?
[HANGE]
If the Third Years win,
I'm totally allowed to
break this open, right?
Please say I am!
Oh, pretty please!
[EREN laughs]
Uh?!
[ALL scream]
Great. Damn it,
Four Eyes. Ugh.
[EREN sighs]
We're never gonna be done.
[RICO] Excuse me.
There aren't enough brooms.
What d'you mean? Should
be enough for every-- Uh!
What are you guys doing here?
Hey. We're human.
We dealt with our share of
uppity upperclassmen back when.
You're not the only ones
who get sick of lectures.
Wait, so, then you guys
know what it's like?
[RICO]
Oh, yeah.
Even though last year
Levi and the others won
by a huge margin,
they still helped us out.
This will go a lot faster
if we divide and conquer.
[RICO]
Right! Let's get a move on!
I want this finished!
[EREN]
Guys!
[ALL]
Mm?
[EREN]
We're sorry!
We should've shown more respect!
Do not misinterpret
our intentions!
We're not here to
soften our image.
We just like to see a
job well done. [groans]
Speaking of Levi and the
others, where are they?
I regret nothing!
[LEVI] Stop running away
from me, Four Eyes!
[ARMIN]
At night,
the screams of Eren and the
others echo through the halls.
The Scouts' traditional
test of courage
is held in spookiest
place on campus,
overseen by a faculty advisor.