All right, guys.
We need to decide what we're
gonna do for the big festival.
Every class has to
arrange two things:
a snack stand and
something else.
I vote maid café!
[YMIR]
Huh?!
[CHRISTA]
Sorry, Brass Band Club's
already doing one of those.
Screw that! We should
totally put on a play!
I know the perfect actor
to play Prince Charming!
[ARMIN]
Hang on.
We don't have enough students
to run two things, right?
I suppose that means some of us
will have to pull double duty.
[MARCO]
Pretty much.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but isn't the highlight the big
B-grade gourmet competition
all the snack stands
have to compete in?
Oo, oo! I know!
Our stand can do perfectly
steamed potatoes!
--I'm thinkin' fried chicken.
--[thud]
[CONY, SASHA]
Uh?
[MIKASA]
Eren?
We're gonna sell cheeseburgers!
[EREN laughs]
This is it, guys!
Our once-in-a-lifetime
chance to show the world
how awesome cheeseburgers
really are!
Don't let it go to waste!
We're closin' in on
being ready, yeah?
Almost! Hold your horses,
it takes a gal time to
get properly prepared!
[ARMIN] Hey. Uh, is it
necessary to go... this far?
Of course it is!
We're not gonna move
a lot of product
with an unsightly staff, are we?
Exactly!
And, if I may point out, last
year's winner is next door.
[HANNA]
They sure are!
[MINA] When they take
the lid off that rice pot,
magic happens.
[FRANZ] I heard so many
customers were lined up
they practically had a
full-scale riot on their hands.
Something I want you
to be aware of, Jaeger.
Our stand's going to win
this competition, bar none.
We are undisputed.
You just keep that
lodged in your mind.
Yeah?! You don't scare me!
Ha! Bring it!
Our cheeseburgers aren't gonna
go down without a fight!
Okay, people! Let's show
'em all how it's done!
[FRANZ, HANNA, MINA]
Yeah!
[HANNA]
Okay, now we do your makeup.
Try to hold still.
[ARMIN]
To be perfectly honest,
there's very little reason to
suppose this plan will work.
I may be naïve,
but there's one thing
I know beyond all doubt.
Sometimes, to win,
we have to accept the burden
of doing the unspeakable.
The pressure to outperform
the reigning champions
is tremendous.
To beat them,
I must be a man who can give
up even his school uniform!
Welcome, everybody!
Who wants to satisfy
their hunger
with a tasty cheeseburger?
[CROWD]
Yeah!
[FRANZ]
Ah...
[HANNA grunts]
[JEAN]
Mirror, mirror, on the wall.
Who's the most popular
student of all?
Uh, I mean... person?
I must tell you, all right:
'tis without a doubt Snow White.
[JEAN] What? But I, Jean,
uh, I mean your Queen
should be the most popular!
You there! Huntsman!
Take this Snow White into
the woods and, well...
Surely you don't need me to
spell it out for you, right?
My Queen.
I shall treat the maiden
to a banquet of wild boar!
[JEAN]
Stop improvising!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Allow me to put a magic
spell on your omelet rice
to make it even tastier.
Abracadabra! Become delicious!
Kindly eat every last bite.
[REINER]
I'm gonna marry her.
[REINER screams]
[BERTHOLDT]
Oh, is that not cool, man?
You can trade with
me if you want.
No, she asked me to finish it,
so that's what I'll do.
Another omelet rice, please!
[CHRISTA]
Okey-dokey!
Another tasty magic
spell coming up!
Abracadabra! Become delicious!
[REINER]
Marry her.
[CHRISTA]
Kindly eat every last bite.
[REINER]
Hey! Don't you touch it!
[YMIR]
Uh?
Reiner, no!
I'll be fine.
I've survived worse
than this. Way worse.
I will eat Christa's
omelet rice!
We will. Together.
[YMIR growls]
Oh yeah? What if I--!
[CHRISTA]
Stop! You're being mean!
Talk to me. Are you okay?
Damn right I am.
If I save only one omelet rice,
it's a good day.
[I'm not sure what that's
supposed to mean,
but it sounds cool!
[REINER yells]
What's happening?
No! So that red stuff
was Tabasco?
[CHRISTA]
Huh?
Look, honey, to tell
you the truth,
I'm not all that into it
either, it's just, y'know.
So, you get it. Good.
[HITCH]
Come on!
You promised we'd go
to this thing together!
You love this crap.
Don't try to hide it.
I'm on to you girlfriend.
[CAT meows]
[ANNIE, HITCH]
Huh?
[meows]
[HITCH]
OMG! Gah! She's so adorable!
Whoa! She's so fluffy!
[gasps] Huh? The
heck's going on?
Kitty want her toy?
Here you go, cuteness.
Come and get it.
[HITCH laughs]
[ANNIE]
Uh?
Who's a fluffy widdle
kitty? You are.
You are.
Ow, that hurt!
Why don't you watch
where you sit?
Ugh! Marlo!
So, Hitch.
Exactly how long have
you been a cat lover?
I'm not a cat lover!
I'm practicing dominance!
You've gotta show the little
fleabags who's boss!
Here, kitty!
Kneel down before me
if you want your toy!
She's ignoring me.
I'd like to buy all the white
tuna you have in stock,
please and thank you!
Well it's clear who the dominant
one in this relationship is.
Hey, guys!
Welcome to the
Cheeseburger Stand,
may I take your order?
Uh! What the hell
is going on here?!
Sorry. Didn't mean
to frighten you.
Eren, Mikasa. It's time
to switch places,
so you guys go do the play and
I'll make myself useful here.
[EREN]
I'm not going.
[SASHA] But you two are
supposed to be the horse's rear
in the next scene!
We're in the midst of
a battle. Look at this.
Until the world understands how
amazing cheeburgs really are,
I'm gonna wrap
every last one!
I go where Eren goes.
If he stays, so do I.
I've got his back whether
he likes it or not.
So just deal with it.
Wow! The way you
dedicate yourself
to cheeseburgers is
utterly inspiring!
I can't do that much, but I'd
sacrifice my time to the cause!
[ARMIN laughs]
I'm staying, too!
[CONNY] There's someone
sleeping on the ground!
[MARCO] Her cheeks are like
roses, her skin white as snow!
I think she may even
be a princess!
[CONNY] Kinda unfair all
you gotta do is lay there,
just sayin'.
It's not my fault Armin
decided not to show up.
Apparently the chee-burg
stand is doing really well.
Oh, and no offense,
but you're a complete
disaster in that outfit.
Hey, hey! Shut your face
and say your lines!
Okay.
Naturally I'd like to start with
the standard battery of test
we conduct on all such captures.
Goochi-goochi-goo!
Tickle monster alert!
[MOBLIT] Hange, please!
Don't get so close!
Aw, c'mon Sawney.
Doesn't it tickle even a
little bit? You can tell me!
Well, go on. Speak.
[HANGE yelps, laughs]
For the love of god:
stand clear!
[laughs] You were
a hair's breadth
from getting me there, darling!
Do you want to get your
head chomped off?!
Well hello there.
All right, ten cheeseburgers
coming up!
[HANNA] I need 20 more
with ketchup, stat!
Chop-chop!
I've got 30 hold the pickle,
fast as you can!
I'm not sure even Mikasa
can handle this many!
[RICO]
Order up! Thirty kamameshi!
[EREN, MIKASA gasp]
[RICO]
Thank you! Come again!
Ian, 50 more orders
of kamameshi, please.
Make the rice extra crunchy.
Comin' right up!
[EREN growls]
Ugh! Way things are goin'...
[MIKASA]
Don't worry.
[gasps]
Mikasa?
[ALL]
Whoa.
She's got this! Right!
Keep those orders
comin' everybody!
[MINA, SASHA]
Yes, sir!
[REINER]
What's up? How we doin'?
Oh, hey!
Don't get too comfy,
but word on the street
is you're neck-and-neck
with last year's champions.
The whole school smells
like cheeseburgers.
Everybody's got
'em on the brain.
Oh, that's just silly:
what does me having Franz on
the brain have to do with it?
[FRANZ]
Come on!
So what if I happen to
think about Hanna 24/7?
[EREN growls]
[CONNY]
Yeah, only problem is
since Armin no-showed Jean's the
one stuck playin' Snow White.
[ARMIN]
What?
[MARCO] Hello, dearie.
Would you like an apple?
[JEAN] My! What a scrumptious
looking piece of fruit!
Why are you and me
the only ones here?
The rotation system we all
agreed on went a little haywire,
so....
Be my guest, young lady.
[JEAN]
Thank you, kindly crone.
Stay here. I'll go
round up some help.
Do what you gotta do
to keep the play going.
Sure, fine. Just come back.
[groaning]
[cackles] At last,
Snow White is no more!
Yes! Now the most popular
person in all the land is I!
[MARCO]
Sorry, Jean! Keep it together!
[HANGE laughing]
Hange, is it necessary
for you to laugh?
Just how do you expect
me to keep from it?!
Ah, ha. Look at him!
Poor thing's absolutely
beside himself!
Aw, stay strong Beane!
That's my boy!
Oh. Look at his face, Moblit!
He's on the verge of
losing it! This is it!
Hurry up and sketch
his expression!
Dang it! It's going
back to normal!
[MOBLIT] Hange! Have you
no compassion at all?
[MARCO gasps]
This crowd is insane!
End o' the line right here!
Get your chee-burg!
[MARCO]
Conny!
Oh! Hi, Marco! Good timing!
The play's gonna tank!
You guys were supposed--
Here, hold this sign
for a few minutes.
I gotta go pee. 'Kay now, bye!
Hold up! Conny!
Hey there, Marco. Say, is
this you kids' snack stand?
Um, yes it is.
The fact we've had to
wait in line this long
means it's super awesome.
Trust me.
You can't tell if
the food's good
just by the size of
the line. Trust me.
People are sayin' they've got
a really cute server
girl on staff.
[ARMIN]
Thanks for waiting!
[ALL gasp]
[PETRA]
A-Armin?
[ARMIN] Here are the four
cheeseburgers you ordered!
Hope you enjoy them!
What the--?
Why in the world are
you dressed like that?
[ARMIN laughs]
Please tell me the
cute server girl
you were just talkin'
about isn't him.
Insolent brat!
How dare you make my
delicate taste buds wait
an inordinate amount of time
to satisfy their cra--!
Stop yammering
and eat already.
Th-This is!
A perfect marriage of
melty cheese and fresh,
high-quality, juice-filled beef.
The meat must've been
tenderized with a knife
and aged to a rich
flavor-- [groans]
[PETRA]
That's what you get
for flapping your jowls
while eating.
[laughs]
[IAN]
Rico. It's just about done.
[RICO]
Excellent!
[ARMIN]
Their method is incredible.
The rice starts on low,
ends on high.
And the lid stays
on till it's done.
Judging from the heat,
they'll be finished
any minute now.
[ARMIN]
Eren! We need to have a sale!
Huh? What kind of sale
are we talkin' about?
We're almost giving
'em away as it is!
[The price point stays
the same. Heh, but...
Now, we'll pack on
double the cheese.
You mean double cheeseburgers?!
[SASHA]
'Scuse me.
I feel like I'm gonna come
down with a stomach ache
right around that time,
so uh, can I man the line?
[MIKASA]
Like hell.
Come on!
What's the big deal?
Look at the crowd. I mean,
clearly we're winning.
For now. But any second,
the tide can turn.
When they remove that lid,
all bets are off.
[SASHA]
He's got a point, you know.
There's nothing like the
smell of slow-cooked rice.
It won't have anything
on the smell of our
freshly-made chee-burgs!
Okay! Double the cheese!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[JEAN] Oh, Princess!
How beautiful you are!
Your raven-black hair,
your rosy-red lips.
You look for all the world
as though only asleep.
[JEAN grunts]
[JEAN]
Dammit! If don't kiss this thing
I can't call myself a prince!
Oh fair one! Let me awaken you
with the kiss of true love.
[STUDENTS]
Whoa!
Hey! I'm acting!
[JEAN groans]
What's that?
It's from next door.
[ARMIN]
Oh no! Can it already be done?
[EREN growls] Damn you, Home of
the Shared Pot, Kamameshi Stand!
[CONNY] Check it out!
They're poppin' the lid!
Engage!
Attention, everyone!
For a special limited time
only we're offering...
Double cheeseburgers
with double the cheese
for the price of a single!
[CROWD cheering]
I've never seen so many
customers in my life!
[MIKASA] Sasha, did you just
slip something into your pocket?
I don't even like chee-burgs.
What are you talking about?
[REINER]
Here they come!
[BOY STUDENT A]
Three double cheeseburgers here!
[BOY STUDENT B]
I'll take ten!
[ORUO]
I'll take 17!
[MOBLIT]
Two for me, please!
[SASHA]
Let me have at least one!
[MIKASA]
No.
Not bad, for a rookie.
Ian, I say it's about
time we open the lid.
Uh?
What is that?
[CONNY]
Uh...
[ARMIN whimpers]
The hell's that noise?
Look sharp, Nile.
Deploy the entire
staff immediately.
We have to assume that a Titan
is about to rear its head.
[NILE]
Huh?!
Titans incoming! Evacuate!
[CROWD screams]
[EREN growls]
[MIKASA gasps]
Eren!
You bastards!
I will destroy you all!
[JEAN] Run, Chee-burg!
Are you out of your mind?!
[EREN yells]
Oh, no! It looks like they're
after the snack stands!
This is bad!
[BOY STUDENT C]
That's our sausage stand!
[GIRL STUDENT A]
Our octopus dumpling stand!
Put those down!
Uh. You really shouldn't
do this alone!
[EREN] You're not gonna
touch another snack stand!
I won't let you ruin
this festival!
Uh!
[ARMIN, SASHA gasp]
Eren!
[EREN groaning]
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[EREN]
No. Give them back!
They took my...
They took our chee-burgs!
Damn you, Titans!
[ARMIN] And just like that.
Everything changed.
At that terrible moment,
in our hearts, we knew.
Junior High was a pen.
The students, cattle.