[ARMIN humming]
[ARMIN]
Isn't this exciting?
It's stupid.
If I'd known the Scout Regiment
was strictly off the books,
I would've signed up for
anything 'sides Wall Cleanup.
[ARMIN]
Who'd have thought, right?
You gotta wonder what kind of
activities this club entails.
[ARMIN]
I think it'll be great!
Sucks we have to start
when it's getting' all hot.
[ARMIN]
Summer's just around the corner.
Yeah, about that.
[ARMIN]
Hm?
[EREN] Aren't you, like,
burning up in that thing?
[ARMIN] Not really.
My hood might look warm,
but matter of fact,
it's made of mesh!
[ARMIN] Neat, huh? Levi
sewed this for me actually.
[CONNY grunts]
Oh, great. What is it now?
[EREN]
Who cares about Armin's hood?
When we're stuck with
Wall Cleanup Club!
I can't be the only one here
who wants to say forget
this and turn around!
My whole thing is
fighting Titans,
which means I need
to get stronger,
something I'm not gonna be
able to do playin' janitor!
[SASHA laughs]
If you quit, they'll
just put you in a club
you're bound to hate even more.
We don't even know what the
Wall Cleanup Club's all about.
At least give it a
chance before you bail.
Yeah, and all the cool clubs
are probably at max
capacity by now anyway.
I'm starting to think
I should've signed up
for the Going Home Club.
Uh, pretty sure that one
only exists in your mind.
What?! Come on,
exactly how many
secret organizations
does this school have?!
[laughs] Well, if
they're secret...
[RICO] Snap to, First Years!
We're not here to gab!
Who the heck is that?
[RICO]
Welcome, new members.
I am the president of
this club, Rico Brzenska.
Brace yourselves, rookies.
You're about to be
put through the mill.
Excuse me. What's all this?
Standard issue custodial
equipment set.
Use it with caution.
Uh! They're just household
cleaning supplies.
Get ahold of yourself! Breathe!
In the glory days when this
club was first founded,
we boasted a hundred members.
Now, I'm the only one left.
This institution needs fresh
blood: in other words, you.
[gasps]
The training will be hard.
That I can guarantee.
[EREN whimpering]
Listen up! As First
Years, you start here!
I want to see these
windows sparkle!
Come on! Seriously?
Doesn't the school have
someone on its payroll
to handle this crap?
[RICO] If you don't like it,
find another club.
But let me warn you.
All of the human
clubs have reached
their membership quotas
for the semester.
The only ones still
accepting applications
are all overrun with Titans.
Uh!
[RICO] By all means,
don't let me stop you.
[ARMIN]
Seems fairly cut and dry to me.
We'd best pick up our
buckets and get cleaning.
[RICO] Start with the new
building. Do not slack off.
If I'd have stuck with
the original plan,
odds are my name
would be synonymous
with Titan Slayer by now.
I'd kill for an afternoon snack.
I bet the Going Home club
has all kinds of snacks.
Stop writing on the windows
and clean 'em already.
You heard what she said.
We can't slack off.
[sighs] See those guys?
I'm so jealous.
[REINER yells]
[BERTHOLDT groans]
What I wouldn't give
to be in their shoes.
[GIRL A giggles]
Seriously,
who joins a club where
they clean windows?
[GIRL B]
Maybe they're being punished
for forgetting their
homework or something.
[GIRL A] You're probably right.
What a bunch of losers!
[JEAN growling]
[ARMIN]
Uh, Jean?
[JEAN] This club is lame!
I'm outta here!
[ARMIN]
Wait! We're on the third floor!
Knock it off, Jean!
We're not even done yet!
Heh. You idiots wanna
shine windows
for the rest of your
lives, be my guest.
[RICO] First Year! I clearly
told you not to slack off!
[JEAN groans]
[RICO]
When I give you an order,
I expect you to see it
through to the bitter end,
is that understood?
We clean whatever the cost.
[EREN]
Rico!
[gasps]
What you just did was
unbelievably awesome!
You were totally
flying like a bird!
I'd be interested to know
how you pulled it off.
That is the coolest thing ever!
You mean this old thing?
We call it Omni Directional
Mobility Gear.
The club's most coveted secret.
[RICO]
It's used like this.
All the better to help scour
down those hard-to-reach places.
[ALL]
Whoa!
[EREN]
If I learn to use this,
it can help me bring
down the Titans!
[JEAN]
If I learn to use this,
I'll be the coolest
guy on campus!
[RICO grunts]
Now quit screwin' around,
those windows aren't
going to clean thems--
[BOTH] Please teach us
how to use your gear!
[EREN]
I get to go first!
[JEAN] Whatever, jerkwad!
Stop copying me!
[ARMIN]
Both of you, calm down!
[SASHA] If they're gonna
be morons, I'll go first!
[CONNY] I see what you
did there! No way!
Wow. I'm dealing with
a pack of idiots.
[RICO]
I appreciate the enthusiasm,
but until you can learn to
clean a window properly,
ODM gear is out
of bounds. Period.
Now, put aside juvenile things
and make a mental note.
You are to clean as though
your lives depended on it.
Show me you understand
by getting back to work!
[ARMIN laughs]
Guess she told us, didn't she?
I suppose we'd better go
back to scrubbing windows.
Don't you get it?
[ALL]
Hm?
If we can show Rico we know
how to take window cleaning
seriously, and she'll teach
us how to use the gear!
Stand back, everybody!
I'm gonna make these windows
shine like they're on fire!
[MIKASA] If that's how you feel
about it, I'm right behind you.
[JEAN]
Hey, hold up!
[SASHA] I want to make 'em
shine like they're on fire!
[CONNY]
Me, too!
[ARMIN]
I'm inspired!
[RICO]
Ugh. Idiotic First Years.
The Wall Cleanup Club is
just a joke to those brats.
Right. Checkup.
I'd better not see so
much as a streak...
Good heavens!
What is this blinding,
angelic light?
[EREN]
Rico!
[RICO gasps]
[JEAN, SASHA, CONNY chuckle]
It's so beautiful.
Well done! Bravo!
Normally only Second
and Third Years
are allowed to use ODM gear,
but in your case I'll
make an exception.
So we...?
Yes!
I'd be honored to teach you all
how to soar through the air!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Okay.
Why am I--? How do
I work this thing?
This can't be happening!
[RICO] What is your major
malfunction, Jaeger?
Now straighten yourself up!
[MIKASA] Just remember the
basics and you should be fine.
[ARMIN]
Loosen up your stance a bit.
If I could do it,
I know that you can!
[EREN]
That's it! I'm going to do it.
I have to! I may not be
as talented as the rest,
but nobody,
nobody has more guts!
I'm not giving up.
Not without a fight!
[ARMIN]
Whoa!
[EREN]
I did it. I freakin' did it!
[EREN laughs]
[EREN gasping]
[ARMIN gasps]
[EREN groans]
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[RICO] Never in my life have I
seen a kid with less aptitude.
[ARMIN]
Eren's so athletic, though.
Something must be
throwing him off.
[JEAN]
What's your trick, tough guy?
You've screwed up in
every way imaginable
short of an accidental
equipment-related asphyxiation.
Face it man,
I'm better than you.
I mean, it's no
big deal, really.
Some people are just
born with skill.
[CONNY]
Woo-hoo! First one up the wall!
[SASHA]
I'm right behind you!
[JEAN]
Hey! Quit showing off!
Ah. Look at 'em! Those jerks!
Getting mad about it isn't
going to solve a thing.
There's time to get some
practice in tomorrow morning.
Either way, to stay in the club,
he has to master the gear.
Wall Cleanup is only for
students with balance.
Uh! What happens if he sucks?
[RICO]
What do you think happens?
He'll be put in some other club.
Uh? No, please!
Just give me a chance!
I don't make the rules.
The weak simply
have no place here.
Oh, no.
I'm pathetic. How am I
supposed to fight the Titans
if I can't even
stand up straight?
It might be time to
let that dream die.
[EREN gasps]
What do you mean?
I think you should give up
this attempt to be a hero.
What're you saying? After
everything we saw that day,
everything the Titans
took from us?!
You're nuts if you think
I'm just gonna walk away!
[MIKASA] Look. It doesn't
matter how determined you are.
Huh?! What are you
talkin' about?!
Because whether
or not you are fit
to be a window cleaner,
isn't up to you.
Setting Jean aside,
even Conny's mastered
the ODM gear.
So clearly it's not a question
of intellect or equilibrium.
Perhaps there's some undetected
flaw in the gear itself?
That's ridiculous!
Our predecessors took a 107
years to perfect this equipment!
When the R&amp;D ran out, they
dug into their own pockets.
They went without juice, man!
They went without juice!
[ARMIN] They really
wanted the wall clean.
There is no chance of
this gear being flawed.
Whatsoever. It is
the fruit of genius!
In fact, I'm so confident that
the gear cannot be to blame,
I'm willing to
stand upside down
and eat spaghetti
through my nostrils--
[RICO] Oh. Well, that's
the problem right there.
[MIKASA]
What's the matter?
[RICO screams]
[MIKASA] I'm no expert,
but, I mean, it looks to me
like the gear he has on
is absolutely to blame.
[RICO]
Oh crap! What am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do?
[HANNES]
Somebody messin' with you?
[EREN]
Hey Mr. Hannes.
Or you just get on
Mikasa's bad side today?
[EREN]
No! What makes you think that?!
Ugh! You smell like booze!
What a minute, what are
you even doing here?!
Huh? What're you
talking about, son?
Who the heck you think
the faculty advisor
is for this club?
[EREN]
What?! You've got to be kidding!
[HANNES]
Shut up.
Take that rig off,
let me have a crack at it.
Uh. I don't--
[EREN]
Do you know what you're doing?
[HANNES]
C'mon. Give me some credit, huh?
They didn't put me in charge
of the Wall Cleanup Club
yesterday, you know.
[RICO]
Excuse me.
[HANNES] There we are. All
right. Now, then. Pay attention
and this old dog might just
teach you some new tricks.
Whoa! Look at Mr. Hannes go!
He's amazing!
So he's not just your average
everyday boozehound!
[laughing] What do you think
of me now? Am I cool or what?
[screams]
Don't even act like you
weren't just trying to cheat!
I found the spot first!
I called dibs!
You both heard me!
That's adorable. Sorry, Jean.
All's fair in love and
housekeeping. Calling dibs.
It's first come,
first serve, doofus!
I'm onto you, Potato Girl!
Don't bring your
hunter's logic into this!
[SASHA]
Potato?!
[HANNES screaming]
[BOTH scream]
[BOTH groaning]
[EREN]
Mr. Hannes! Are you okay?
[HANNES]
Eren.
There's nothing you could've
done about this rig,
you understand?
You're a kid. You're weak.
[EREN] Actually, I was
practicing earlier.
Don't beat yourself
up. I'm far worse.
When push came to shove I
was just too hammered!
[EREN]
Ugh! You reek!
[RICO yells]
Mr. Hannes, what have you done?
The gear was perfectly fine!
[HANNES]
Huh? Well I'll be damned.
Ah, you're such a mess.
Whatever are we to do with you?
I'll have to mend that
rig myself after class.
That's it for today,
everyone! We're done here!
[MIKASA]
What's got you so worked up?
[RICO]
None of your bees wax!
I said we're done!
Go home, or wherever!
[RICO]
Eren Jaeger. Are you ready?
[EREN]
Yes!
I can do it now! Yeah-ah!
I don't know what's
different from yesterday
but I've totally got this now!
[SASHA]
Congratulations, Eren!
[CONNY]
Way to go, man!
Well, Rico?
This mean I can stay?
I can be in the
Wall Cleanup Club?
Uh. Yes, you passed.
Nice job! Now keep training.
[EREN]
Check it out, Mikasa!
I'm doin' it!
I can fight the Titans!
You don't have to worry
about me anymore!
I'm actually glad things
worked out for him.
His eyes are definitely
saying 'Check me out!'
Nuh-uh.
[ALL]
Mm?
What his eyes are
really saying is
he doesn't have to leave me.
At least, not anymore.
[ALL]
Uh...
What the...?
[JEAN] Okay. Do I wanna
know what you're doing?
[SASHA] Gigantic footsteps
headed this way! Super-fast!
[CONNY]
Huh?!
[RICO growls]
Move away from the wall! Now!
[RICO]
The Titans are coming!
Stay where you are.
What are they doing?
What's with the spray paint?
[gasps]
They're tagging the
wall. Those jerks!
That's terrible!
Yes. Now you see what
we're dealing with.
Their graffiti is the reason
this club was founded.
Someone had to clean up
the widespread vandalism.
It's an eyesore.
Several students decided to take
matters into their own hands.
Their names were
Alyosha, Dominic,
Fine, Isabel, Ludwig,
Martina, Guido, and Hans.
The founding members of
the Wall Cleanup Club.
[EREN]
Sorry, I have to do this.
Eren, wait!
Don't be a fool, Jaeger!
[grunts] Did someone teach that
boy how to use his ODM rig
while my back was turned?
[RICO growls]
[EREN yells]
I can do this!
As long as I'm
wearing this gear,
the Titan's don't have a prayer!
[MIKASA]
Eren!
Way to go.
Uh, guess it goes to show you
how important practice is.
I've bitten off more
than I can chew.
He'll have to be
trained from scratch.
Yeah!
Yeah, you better run! Next time
you won't have it so easy!
[ARMIN]
Test scores.
A hardship that plagues
all students equally,
whatever their status,
whatever their skill.
To escape the despair
of remedial courses,
Sasha asks Armin for help,
with mixed results.