[Heavy breathing]
You can't get away, kid!
Don't make it hard on yourself.
Be a good boy and hand
that No. 2 headband
over nice and slow like.
Stop right there, kiddo!
You draw that sword
and you're dead.
What the hell is with you, kid?
You've got to learn
to respect your elders.
Lookie here.
Now I'm the No. 2 warrior.
I'm comin' for ya, No. 1!
What the hell is this?
This kid is really
some kinda freak!
He's carryin' a rotten head
around in his backpack!
Agh! Wait a minute,
I know that guy!
That's the old No. 1.
Yeah, you're right.
Here, give it to me.
[laughing]
Whoa!
Heh, heh, heh, you
want this back, kiddo?
Then catch!
Kids these days.
Yeah, they got no respect.
--Let's go.
--Yeah, heh, heh...
Wake up, wake up, wake up!
Oh, sleepy head!
Jinno! Jinno!
Wow, check this out.
Some piece of work!
He won't wake up, Jinno!
What? Whoa!
Master, master!
The bandits must have got him!
This is bad!
Two guys yesterday
and now a kid.
He is not a morning person.
Oh my god, he's alive.
Master! Master! He's alive!
[chuckles] He's just sleepy!
Don't get up yet.
You've been badly
wounded and poisoned.
It will take some
time for you to recover.
We discovered you
bleeding on the riverbank.
It's a miracle you didn't drown
with your arm so badly broken.
I am called Okiku.
I can take care of you.
Rest, mighty samurai.
Don't be alarmed, of course
we know you're a samurai.
For who else but a samurai
could clutch his sword
in a raging river
while poisoned,
unconscious, and
with a broken hand?
Sleep. When you awake,
I'll have a meal prepared.
Damn, you one lucky dog, Afro!
[chuckles]
You look like a mummy!
Cut it out, Otsuru!
Do not worry, young Afro.
In my dojo, we are all wounded
orphans. You are among friends.
Treat him well, my students.
Yes, master.
Go! Go! Go!
Strike the ground
with yourself!
How can you wield a sword
if you can't dig a hole?
You're mad at the dirt, Jinno?
Your body is all stiff.
Think less... Relax.
I'll stay calm and flowing,
like a river, humph!
Cheer up, Afro.
Oh, I see we up!
Think I wasn't
going to find you?
I just took a little R&amp;R,
but look at you, boy!
All bright-eyed
and bushy tailed!
Fish, flowers, sunshine!
I see somebody's getting
their lil' resort on! Ha, ha!
Wooo, I betcha that babe,
wh-what's her name?
Okiku. I bet she tastes a hell
of a lot better than trout!
Don't think I didn't notice her
checking you out! Uh? Uh?
Don't tell me...
You ain't noticed?!
Sh... This place is bananas!
I'm thinking, shit...
I'll even go find me a little
hottie to kick it with...
Feed me some cold noodles....
...massage me,
...get all sweaty...
You know what I mean?
If she's got a friend,
maybe we can do an orgy,
you know? Huh? Huh?
Awight-awight, awight-awight...
So you ain't the
swingin' type... awight.
Still, I'm getting' my sex on.
You know, getting
your Jimmie waxed
just might help you recuperate.
Awight-awight, you relax!
You want to do your night
solo on the low low...
Cool.
Don't forget--my cellie is off.
You must not fight over food.
Come on, Afro.
We're all waitin' on you, dude.
We've got fishing duties down at
the river, don't you remember?
We're gonna be late.
Ah, you know how everyone gets
when there's not enough
fish to eat around here.
Look, I don't mean to push, but
you really oughta wolf it down,
we'll need all your strength.
Tricking fish ain't easy!
Tricking fish ain't easy..
Wolf 'em down! [chuckles]
Come on!
Let's get to it!
[laughter]
Look, they're escaping.
Let's grab 'em.
--Yeah!
--Let's grab 'em!
You ready for this, Otsuru?
Fishie!
Nice and fat, just like
the doctor ordered.
It's what the master
calls the single beat.
Well, cook it up, then we
can have a quadruple treat.
But there's six of us... isn't
that a ... sextuplet... treat?
Huh?
I mean...
[laughter]
Oh, I must have disturbed
you in the middle of a dream.
Was it pleasant?
Forgive me, I'm being nosy.
It's time for your medicine.
Your wounds heal well,
master samurai.
So, tonight I will cook
my special fish for you.
You do like fish, don't you?
Huh! Huh! Huh!...
Fresh vegetables?
Not interested, kid. Beat it.
Ah, no luck today.
Let's go home, Afro.
So, about
No. 2... Is it true?
That's what they say.
Apparently he's back in town.
Maybe I'll give it a shot.
Whatever.
Like you got what it takes
to be the No. 2
warrior of the world!
What the fuck?
What's this kid doing here?
Where is the No. 2?
Who?
The No. 2 headband.
Tell me who has it.
Umph, I don't know
what you're talking about!
Ugh!![scream]
Tell me where he is.
You little cocksucker!
[grunting sound]
You think you're a killer, boy?
Huh?!
I'll show you a killer!
When you fight to kill...
Finish the job.
Target is confirmed.
Yes... he's still injured...
An easy prey for my skills.
Yes, I understand your point.
But my master brother,
I would give my life to
work in your inner circle...
Can you do it?
Yes, please let me
slay the Afro Samurai.
Urghh....
Supper is ready.
What's the matter?
Thanks for everything.
You're leaving?
Tomorrow...
Please, keep it
for your travels.
Katajikenai.
Will you not stay with me?
For just one more day?
There'll be a summer festival
tomorrow night
at the village below.
If it's not too much to ask,
will you stay and watch
the fireworks with me?
Foolish boy.
Never speak to me
of such things again.
Games of power... revenge...
they lead to nothing!
Do you really know what
it means to be the No. 2?
It is a life of murder.
We are born MEN in order
to live, not to kill!
You must break the chain...
Only then can we be
free of this terrible cycle.
What is this?
Swamp water...
Just try it!
Will it put hair on my chest?
Ew, it tastes like crap!
Here, Afro, you try it.
[gulping]
Looks like this boy is the
only one with real taste.
Can I have some more?
Is he for real?
Afro, you don't
have to be polite.
It's like I always say, if
heaven could be bottled...
...it just might taste
like my lemonade.
Lenemode!
Lemonade...
Lemonade...?
Lemonade!
Lemonade.
Hey, kid... We know it was
you that killed our brother.
Too bad you have to pay for it!
You little son of a bitch!
What the... Huh?
Hey, that's my... knife.
How did you...?
You little...
Aghhh!
You ain't gonna
get away from me!
This can't be, ugh!
--I got him.
--Good!
Don't let him get away!
Now, let's see you spit
swamp water, brat!
He, heh, he...
you are dead now.
Hey, shorty!
What was that?
What did you just call me?!
Oh, shit!
Afro!
--Yahh!
--Leave him alone!
Behind you!
Afro!
Fucking brats!
What the--
Shit! It's stuck...
Dammit!
I'll kill you...
Holy smoke!
Killing some little kid
is normally against
my principles...
But, when you cut
my pal's brother...
...you entered the
world of killin', boy!
Before I kill you,
remember this!
If you're gonna swing a sword,
you better be ready
to get cut by one too!
Say your prayers... aghh!
Damn it!
You missed.
You piece of shit!
Freakin' kid.. I should have...
Do you know where No. 2 is?
[strained]
What was that?
I want to see No. 2!
What for?
To kill him! I'll kill him!
Stop laughin' and tell me!
He's already dead.
What?
There is a new No 2.
You'll never find him.
He's probably long gone.
Heh, heh...
Yes... yes... no...
I need more time.
I haven't acquired
that data yet.
What I do have has been
downloaded on to my cell phone.
Yes... yes. Understood.
Sorry.
OKIKU!
Are you there?
Yes...
What is the matter,
Disciple Okiku?
Nothing. Everything
will be taken care of.
Yes, hello. Brother 2 here.
Yo, yo, yo, Afro!
Can I ask you something?
Now I know you cast away
your feelings an' all, but...
Does that mean casting
away your manhood too?
Ooh... Mama-sans don't
get much better than ol' girl.
She's sweet. Pretty.
Knows her first aid, can
broil a mean fish dinner...
I'd call that practically
marriage material.
C'mon now, confess...
You want to hit that booty.
I just want to see my
boy happy, you know.
Seriously, man.
Now don't you think
there's something vaguely
familiar about that woman?
Look. If you ain't gonna
knock them boots, I will.
Go on, then...
Care for some?
It's lemonade. Do you like it?
I do.
Good.
Oh, they're beautiful.
This is my favorite
time of the year...
Fireworks and
the festivities...
The people coming and going...
Everyone just simply
having a good time...
So where are you traveling to,
if I may ask?
East.
East...
Oh, I love this kind.
They're my favorite.
It's all because of you!
Forgive me. I've become a
ninja of the Empty Seven clan.
I've been siphoning
your memories
to copy your sword skills!
But I can't...
I can't do it anymore...
To me, you're still
that same boy
from those wonderful
times so long ago.
Get out of my way...
Otsuru!
Lord Afro!
Run!
You fuckin' whore! This is the
price you pay for your betrayal!
The data...
We have obtained the data.
That's enough, Brother 6!
We are leaving!
Damn shame, ain't it?
Just when you start
getting your groove on,
shit's always gotta get killed,
burnt down, or whatever...
Hey, you know, your afro got a
little scorched there, Holmes...
You listenin' to me?
Man. You really are a
cold-blooded motherfucker.
Hey...
How about we keep this little
memento of your lady friend?
Ha, ha, ha!