Wait here, son.
It'll soon be over.
Remember me, No. 1?
I've been waiting a very
long time for this.
I know.
But, it all ends here.
Come on, man.
Gimme whatcha got!
Finally... I've got the
title of No. 1 in my hand.
Do... not... avenge... me.
With this band
across my forehead...
I will rule this world
as God himself!
It's unfortunate that you
had to see this, boy.
This moment will
always haunt you.
You will be consumed
by hatred for me.
Challenge me when you're
ready to duel a god. Heh heh...
Ha, ha, ha...
Yeehaw!
This is the end of the road...
Afro Samurai!
We got 20 guys here--
all armed to the teeth,
We got you surrounded.
We never said we
were gonna play fair!
I got no idea why,
but some pretty rich folk wanna
pay top dollar for that cloth.
Why don't you give it up, kid...
Everybody's a tough guy...
Okay, have it your way.
Gear up, boys!
Look at this, boys! Tough guy
here's gonna take us out
with only one hand
on his sword!
Cut him up!
What the fu--
That's impossible!
You son of a...
Fuckin' fucker!
I cut you! I cut you!
Hmm...
[breathing]
I took this job because...
I thought you were
just a legend...
Just a story... A story
to scare little kids.
But you're the real deal--
the Demon who dares
to challenge God.
So what the hell do you want?!
Don't seem to me
like you out to make this
stinkin' world a better place.
Why you gotta kill all my men?
Why you gotta kill me?
Nothing personal,
it's just revenge.
Yo yo yo yo yo, Afro!
That was off the chain! Cold-
blooded! Damn, motherfucker!
Excuse me for probing, but
what you just did back there,
was it absolutely necessary?
I'm beginning to wonder
if you got any feeling for
human life left in you at all.
[coughs]
Hey, hey, hey. If you
don't stop dissin' me,
I'm gonna stop followin'
your brutal ass around.
Then whose gonna
watch your back?
Anyway,
I did check some monk-looking
bald motherfucker in a tree
chattin' on a celly while
watchin' your killin' spree.
Don't that bother you?
Sure as hell bother me.
Yo! Yo!
Hold up! Hold up!
Afro!
Yo! Yo! Yo!
Breaking news just in!
What the...?
Jeez...
Easy, kid.
What's the problem?
It's HIM! He's here! He's here!
--[murmuring]
--No way!
What the hell are you
talking about, punk?
[heavy breathing]
Ain't no doubt
about it, man. He...
[heavy breathing]
Here. Drink up.
He had this Afro hairdo...
you know what I'm sayin'?
With kind of a
greenish tint to it
if you looked real close...
And he was wearing
this freakin' headband,
with the No. 2 stamped high
across his freakin' forehead...
Did you say Afro-hairdo?
Greenish tint?
The headband... With No. 2
written across it?
Make no mistake...
That's him, that's the No. 2!
The AFRO SAMURAI!
The Afro Samurai...!
The one who cut down the
assassins of the western guild?
Th-The No. 2 swordsman...
of the world?
He's cold-blooded!
He killed the brothers of
Asura in only five moves!
So don't think twice about
crossing swords with that guy...
What a bunch of sissies!
Screw that, cowards!
You guys just watch while I
take that No. 2 headband!
That's all bullshit!
You assholes just watch!
I'm gonna take him out!
It's gonna be me!
Let me take him, baby!
He's all mine.
Nah, I'm gonna be the No. 2!
All y'all just shut up!
Cause while you talk
and talk and talk,
my spear will be splitting
his head in half!
Just like this!
Hey, man!
Get that rusty piece of
junk outta my face, man...
[grunts]
Ma'am...
Yeah?
Why is everyone
after this Afro Samurai?
You don't know? You really
must be from out of town.
We got ourselves a
legend around here.
A legend?
Look. Two ancient headbands.
No. 1 and No. 2.
If you have the No. 1--
you're like a god--
NOBODY can touch you...
Except he who wears... No. 2.
The trouble with THAT is--
The trouble with THAT is,
that anyone in the world
can challenge you.
Clever boy!
You're interested?
The life of No. 2:
constant combat.
But ultimately, the path
a warrior should take
and the reward is
to become a god.
Yep. They say the No. 1
waits at the top of Mt. Shumi.
You can't miss it.
It's got like two huge
hand-like things...
Get outta my way!
Take it easy, Mac!
You ain't the only one here
who thinks he can take him.
Ugh!
Agh!
You caved my eyes in!
Fucking son of a bitch!
You warmed up yet?
Hm...
Hey hey, you wanna fight?
Take it outside!
Mmm...
Lemonade... ice cold.
Coming right up! 250, please.
Lemonade...
Heh, heh, heh...
Hey man, shut the hell up!
Now look who we
got ourselves here...
Here you are... lemonade.
Huh! Drink that, boy!
Uh, another one?
On his tab?
Holy...
Here you are... lemonade.
That's gonna cost
you more than 250.
And I think that guy's
tab has run out.
That's very cool.
Oi-shi... Refreshing...
Good, you'll need it.
You've still got a long
way to go, No. 2!
Cross the mountains by way of
the "Low Down East" path.
Beware the cliffs, and know
that they're waiting for you.
Thanks.
Hey Afro! Yo, Fro-boy.
Your sure this is the
right way to go?
These cliffs don't
look so safe, man.
And one other thing.
Don't look now, but I
think you got a stalker.
A crazy fan boy
from the tea house
and he don't want
your autograph--
more like your epitaph.
Now, I suggest you keep
steppin', cause this one...
...is a stone killer, for real.
Yo, didn't you hear me?
Get going!
I'm trying to pull your coat.
All you gonna do is ignore me?
Alright, alright, you wanna
blow it for me and you, huh?
Shut up...
Well fine, go on, get
your lanky ass killed, then.
But don't say
I didn't warn ya! Later!
I am called Shosun.
I come from the land
of the great weapon
masters of the west.
I see you wear one of
the head bands of legend
that leads to godhood.
So, shall we?
Afro, don't fight this fucker.
He got arrows and
grenades and shit.
You ain't got no chance, dude!
Oh, lord, no no no!
Agh! Is you dead?
Don't tell me you dead!
Is you dead?
I asked you a question!
Your jumping
has only put you
directly in the line of
my fire, samurai fool!
Where will you go now,
great No. 2 warrior?!
My aim is only to move forward!
Whoa! Brother,
you did your thang!
I thought you
was dead for sure!
Yo, my man, I gots to tell ya,
I don't know if it's
your natural pheromones
or you need a shower,
but assassins are comin'
at us like flies on hot shit.
I gots to say, there's something
strange still out there.
Hm... Yes...
It's me! Brother 2.
Yes... uh-huh, I see...
Carry on then.
And remember you are
among the righteous few
and we have placed great faith
in your ability to track him.
Because the No. 2 warrior has
now begun to move in earnest,
it seems our cherished brother's
work is now truly beginning.
The No. 2 walks the
path Low Down East...
In the great
ancestral direction...
Our No. 2 warrior's
journey will no doubt end
at the great valley before
the high slopes of Mt. Shumi.
We're getting almost
all the data we need.
The mandate of heaven has
spoken and agreed with us,
the righteous, the EMPTY SEVEN!
Wash over us, the supreme power!
Let us pay homage
to the Holy Way!
Ahyee a Nonon-Bow...
Let us close our eyes
and feel the power.
Let the Divine roll within you.
Let the Holy Way call you.
As the Divine Will has ordained,
we have risen from the ashes.
From this condition
of oppression,
we have borne the cross,
but we will seize the crown...
and the prophecy shall
be fulfilled--eye for an eye--
No. 2 shall know no mercy at
the hands of the EMPTY SEVEN!
Prepare for the final struggle!
Freedom is in our reach!
The supreme power
of God shall be ours!
Amen!
Have you heard, my brothers?
--Yeah!
--Oh, yes!
Do you hear the word?
--Right!
--Woo!
Man, all these killin's are
really starting to depress me.
You know what I mean, Afro?
Oh, mo' cold shoulder, huh?
Yo, Holmes, you're
walkin' a little funny.
What's up? Whoa, wassup?
Was it something
in the lemonade?
Oh, snap, you
fucked up, Holmes!
Oh look, oh shit, it was
those damn arrows!
Come on, Afro, snap out
of it, man! Snap out of it!
He's injured, I can take him.
What?
Hey, hey! Wait! Wait!
It's too early!
Whoa!
Hey, hey, hey, can't you
give a brother a break, yo?
Can't you see the man is down?
What about honor
and fairness and shit?
Hey, that a motherfuckin' RPG?!
You got a motherfuckin' RPG?!
A RPG in a
motherfuckin' backpack?!
Wait, wait wait, can
we talk about this?
You ain't got a monologue?
You're not gonna give
a bad guy speech?
Oh my god!
Oh my god, oh my god...
That fool!
He may have destroyed the
sacred No. 2 headband as well!