Add one more body
to the body toll.
May God rest this
poor bastard's soul.
Yo, Afro!
Ain't you gonna say nothin'?
I'm talking to you!
I said I'm talkin' to you!
Long time no see, Afro.
Hey correct me if I'm wrong,
but I don't think a teddy bear
is supposed to be
walking around in
a damn kimono
strapped with blades.
I got a baad feeling about this.
You don't want to be messin'
with this guy! Afro!
I'm telling you man,
that shit ain't natural!
He might look cute an' all
but I got a suspicion this
one's a pro! He's for real!
Aw!
Look, I know you've
got mad skills and all.
And I ain't trying
to be pessimistic here,
but you headed
straight to a dirt nap!
Please, this time
you could really bite it.
And I ain't going with you!
You sure about this?
Because if you is...
Suit yourself.
Aww, hey, hey hey hey yo-yo yo
yo, wait up wait up! Hold up!
Damn, you one stubborn samurai!
Come on man, chill.
Listen to what I've got
to say for once, please!
Aw...
Watch it! He's 'bout to bust
a two sword move on you!
Uh-oh.
Watch your left, man! No,
no no no no, watch your right!
Why do you not
draw out your sword?
If you want the No. 1...
You must first defeat me.
You HAVE come to defeat the
No. 1... Haven't you?
Agh! If you wear
the No. 2 band...
Then you must fight!
What the hell?
Perhaps the rumors of the
Afro Samurai are not true...
...that he cuts all
that stand in his path...
that his only
movement is forward...
But you just look like
an Afro-headed coward!
Come to think of it...
I can't even take a warrior
with such stupid hair seriously!
Afro!
What the dilly yo babe?
If you gonna run, run!
If you gonna fight,
then damn it, fight!
Such a fleeting moment in time.
Nothing remains.
Everything ends.
No!
One. There is no
such thing as killing
with strength or speed only.
Kill the enemy with one
calm powerful stroke.
Two. The only form is action.
Striking without thought is the
only way to kill the enemy.
Huh! Huh! Huh!
[sword swinging practice]
Stop!
Listen.
The point of dueling
is to kill your enemy.
Not twisting and turning,
demonstrating flowery form.
The only position
is no position.
Where you hold your sword
depends on your relationship
with your opponent,
on the terrain,
and the situation.
Act as the sea when the
enemy is like the mountain.
Act as the mountain when
the enemy is like the sea.
Keep this in mind, all of you!
--Yes, Master!
Real attacks are not static,
or with cooperative opponents.
Stick with the moves you learned
in class and you will die.
Even a glancing blow can
unbalance your opponent
and cripple his next offensive.
Hey, Jinno? I have a question.
Why do you use two
swords instead of one?
With two I can
be the best, Otsuru.
You see...
There are lots of reasons.
For example, it's great
if you ever have to fight
more than one
opponent at a time.
You see, with 2 smaller blades,
I can swing faster...
than a guy with both
hands on one big sword.
AND... I can attack and
defend at the same time!
I could even fight if one
of my arms got cut off,
cause I'll still have one left!
It's really the ultimate
fighting style.
Huh?
Oops... Sorry. I guess I
got a little carried away.
I'm done.
Was your meal yummy, Afro?
Jinno...
You're really serious about
sword-fighting, aren't you?
Of course.
I have to protect everyone.
You... Afro...
All the students here.
When Swordmaster
is too old to fight...
I'm gonna have to be strong
enough to look after this place.
I heard some pipsqueak's been
running loose killing assassins.
That pipsqueak wouldn't
happen to be a kid
like this one we've
got here, would it?
I think we got a match
here boys. Eh, pipsqueak?
I want to know where
I can find the No. 2.
Don't know nothin' about it.
So what are you
gonna do about that?
Cause you see, we're
on the same path, kid.
Rumors of the No. 2
led us to this dump.
And we can't have no
kid chasing our prize.
Afro!
Jinno.
What have you
gotten yourself into?
Okay. You and I are
gonna talk about this later.
But first I've got
to save your dumb ass.
You son of... Agh....
Afro!
Tell me what you know!
Where's the No. 2?
No. 2 is quite near...
Oh, it's you again...
There you go, sonny.
You just can't get enough
lemonade, can you?
Afro...
Forget avenging your father.
Live your own life..
Otsuru cares about you.
I care about you.
We're your family now.
--Ah! Look at that!
--So beautiful!
Cool!
--Wow!
--Aw, man...
Say, you reckon I can
be as strong as Master?
With your skill, Sasuke,
I'd say it'll take
at least 50 years.
50 years?
[laughter]
--Look!
--Whoa...
--Check out that one!
--Beautiful...
To get as strong as
Master takes time.
His training must have been
100 times harder than ours.
Man... I could be
dead in 50 years...
...or even worse than that, old!
Dead?! Man, Sasuke,
why do you always have
to be so dang morbid?
He is right in a way, though.
I mean, we can't know for sure
if any of us will be around
50 years from now...
...or even 10 years from now...
So there's no use
in worrying about
being as good as
the Swordmaster...
That's why you
always have to live
and fight like
it's your last day.
Or eat like it's
your last meal...
--Cool!
--Nice!
Wow...
They're so bright!
Man, I hope that my last meal
has lots of mushrooms in it!
I want my last meal
to be absolutely
smothered in chili peppers.
Oh man, I could go
for a chicken cutlet.
Afro, what about you?
What do you want?
Afro wants lenemode. Right Afro?
Otsuru, it's lemonade,
not lenemode.
[laughter]
That's not a meal, Otsuru!
--Huh?
--It's okay.
What would you like
on your last day?
I want those!
Those fireworks are
my favorite kind!
Good day, sir.
Well, hello there.
Thank you always for
your kind business with us.
Say, that
Swordmaster of yours...
Is he alright?
Huh?
On the festival evening...
I heard that some rogue tried
to start up a fight with him.
There are some odd
talks around the town
that some sword dojo master
is the owner of the
No. 2 headband,
and they say
that his students
have been brainwashed
to be watchdogs...
What?!
Our Swordmaster wouldn't...
Sorry! Sorry!
I didn't mean to...
I mean, there are plenty of
other Swordmasters everywhere.
So it must be some other man.
Jinno. Did I wake you?
You should get some rest.
Master... I smell blood.
I was attacked. But that
fool lost his life instead.
Sasuke.
Jinno.
Afro.
On this day, we
commemorate your graduation.
You are now great warriors.
Use wisely the sword skills
you have acquired.
Master...
Yes, Afro.
There is something
I would like to know.
Afro.
Are you really No. 2?
After the midnight...
before the bodhi tree...
I will be waiting.
I meant to take the
secret to the grave.
But I see I have no choice.
Choose, Afro Samurai.
Forget revenge,
or fight me to the death...
for the No. 2 headband.
But know you well this truth.
If you win, you will know
no friend, no joy, no love.
Only the murderous violence
the No. 2 headband
incites in the heart
of every man who desires
the power of the No. 1!
Truly, can you
handle that burden?
Afro!
Master?! What's going on?
Master! Please stop!
Afro! What are you doing?
Master?
There he is!
Quit wasting your
time with that kid!
--Jinno...
--Fight us!
That No. 2 headband is mine!
Master!
Jinno, take everyone and run!
Run and live.
Now you will see what it means
to wear the No. 2 headband...
Master!
Fool! Stay out of this!
Stay away from me!
Let's see whatcha got.
[crying]
Playtime's over, kiddies.
Sasuke! No!
Jiro! Matasaburo!
Otsuru!
Jinno!
Afro!
You have chosen your path.
Afro... No...
Don't...
Why?
Why did you kill our master?
What have you done?
He's dead! And you...
you chose revenge...
...over our master...
Over everyone!
We're your family...
Why?
For my true father...
What about us...
What about us?!
I...
...treated you
as my brother...
I will...
...never...
...forgive you!
Jinno!
Hey, Afro.
Who...?
Whatcha waitin' for? You really
sure that's the right decision?
I mean... if you don't
wanna wear it... it's ok, man.
Don't do it man...
seriously, don't do it...
Damn... there goes the
neighborhood... Heh heh heh....
Good.
I'm glad you've lasted this
long. I want you to die slowly.
I want you to burn, bleed,
suffer as I have!
Kuma, what is taking so long?
Just finish him off!
I take orders from no one!
How dare you! You will obey
my orders and finish the Afro!
You must not fail as
the Empty Seven have.
Don't compare me to them.
I don't care about the
useless headband...
I just want Afro!
I want him hurt.
I want him crippled.
He'll bleed for all
the pain he's caused.
Do what you want, then...
You don't know how
long I've waited...
...to avenge the deaths of those
who loved and trusted you!
[mechanical breathing sound]
My tears have never stopped
falling since that day...
Jinno...
Arrgghhhh!