[TAMA yells, gasps]
[crash]
[TAMA whimpering]
[TAMA gasps, crash]
[TAMA] How am I
supposed to get out
when there's not even a door?
[TAMA] Or at least there's
no door that I can see.
[RUKO crying]
Yuki! Wake up! Answer me!
Please! Yuki!
Yuki... Come on...
Please say something, okay?
You can't die!
Yuki!
[TAMA] I'm supposed to
believe there isn't a door,
but that's not true.
There is one.
Right here.
I just have to select it.
[HITOE] We'll be in trouble
if that groundskeeper
finds us in there.
Yeah, but... we have to.
[RUKO crying]
Please... Wake up.
Yuki!
[IONA]
What a sight to see.
Those tears of yours, Ru.
They shine like gems.
They're beautiful.
[IONA] I wanted to be
your LRIG so badly.
You're the strongest
Selector I'd ever encountered.
With you, I knew that
I could defeat anyone
and I longed for it.
I couldn't help my desire.
I was formed from Mayu's sorrow,
darkness, filth,
and pain, after all.
All those horrible feelings,
they echoed in my heart.
But, as I battled
alongside you,
I felt something else.
Your warmth and light.
It did more than just touch me.
It illuminated me
and began to spread.
[IONA]
And as it did...
I felt something beautiful
and precious overcome me.
My heart, however corrupt,
had been born anew.
And best of all,
you showed me something new.
That which I truly desired.
Yuki...
[IONA]
While I can say it, thank you.
Stop!
You don't have
to thank me, okay?
And stop making this sound
like you're saying goodbye!
[MAYU] I don't understand.
Why is she crying?
Parting wasn't
this painful for me.
What is it that
the two of them have?
[URITH]
Aww...
Boo-hoo, you're gonna lose
your special widdle buddy,
as if I gave a damn.
The Battle ends when a LRIG
disappears, so you lose,
unless she's still with us.
So tell us, Iona,
or should I say, "Yuki."
Can you still battle,
or have you vanished?
[TAMA] Ru and Yuki
won't lose to you.
[URITH gasps]
--[MAYU] Shiro!
--[RUKO] Tama!
[MAYU] Impossible!
How did she get out?
Tama...
You can win. Just use Grow.
Make me and Yuki into one.
[IONA]
Tama, no.
There's no need for you
to do something like that.
You can't let me
become a part of you.
I would only corrupt you.
You're not corrupt.
You're pretty.
Sparkling like snow
in the warm sun.
You think so? Really? Me?
[RUKO] Tama is like the sun
that shines in summer.
And you're like the snow
that falls in winter.
[RUKO] So if you guys
come together as one...
...you'll be like snow
falling in the summer.
Now Grow!
Level 5! Mayu!
Wait... What is this?
Why did you call out my name?
[RUKO]
Because Tama is my friend.
Yuki is my friend.
And the one who created
them both is you.
But right now,
you're not my friend.
I don't like you
very much at all
because you made every one of us
who played the game suffer.
Just look.
These people are
in pain because of you.
So many girls, scarred for life.
Not just their bodies,
but their souls too.
But there is a
part of you I do like.
What?
The true you that's
next to me, Tama and Yuki.
I'm sure if this
wasn't how things were,
if we'd somehow met before you
started the Selector Battles,
I would have really liked you.
And we would have been friends.
[MAYU]
Stop it. Shut up!
Is hearing something like that
supposed to make me feel happy?
We would have been friends?
I hate you!
You just want to bury me!
Go, Urith!
Attack with Black Desire!
Yeah! Now you're
talking, partner!
Mayu!
[MAYU (MERGED)]
Ru! Let's battle!
I know it sounds odd,
but even if Selector Battles
themselves are wrong...
They're still our only chance at
winning the other Mayu over,
so we have to do this, okay?
Right!
[KAZUKI grunting]
[pounding noise]
Oh man, what a
sad-looking room.
[RUKO]
Mayu! Summon Arc Energe!
Attack with Laevateinn, go!
Hey, Mayu, are you okay?
Yes.
[MAYU]
No!
Stop it! That's my name!
[MAN'S VOICE]
How's she doing?
[WOMAN'S VOICE] Well, she
has a lack of appetite, again.
[MAN'S VOICE]
Yes, that was expected.
Increase the dosage.
That girl. Her status?
What is she doing?
She's alert?
[MAYU] Ruko said her name
with such concern.
My name was never
spoken that way.
[gasps]
[URITH] Dammit, would you
look at yourself?
Have you forgotten
you're the one
who started the
Selector Battles?
[MAYU]
Selector...
How ironic.
[MAYU] Me? I didn't get
to select anything.
Mayu?
[MAYU] It's not that
I didn't want to.
It's just that I didn't have
any "selections" to make!
That's right. And also...
While it looks like
I took dreams and wishes
away from everyone, I didn't.
I gave all of them the
opportunity to make a choice.
Sure, I know that ended up
hurting some of them in the end,
but at least they had freedom!
But me?
No, I was denied even that!
[YUZUKI] The only thing
that connects this place
to the outside
is that window, you guys.
This tiny room.
It was Mayu's entire world.
I never had a chance to select.
[RUKO]
That's not true.
Now tell me.
Why'd you seal
Tama away like that?
Why let Yuki be the
only one who could battle?
[MAYU]
"Why?"
Because she hated it.
The world outside the window,
a world that was
filled with light.
[MAYU (MERGED)] In reality,
she longed for that world.
She wanted to be a part
of it more than anything.
That's why just when
her life came to an end,
Mayu did indeed
make a selection.
And with it, Tama awakened.
Beyond the wall of black,
beyond the wall of white,
there existed a world
full of countless shades.
Tama, longing for
light like Mayu,
was released into
this colorful new world.
[MAYU]
You're wrong! That's not true!
Lies... All lies.
I wouldn't do that.
That isn't like me!
[RUKO] Why don't you come
see the outside world
with all of us?
We'd love to show it to you.
[MAYU]
How can you say such a thing?
Didn't you hear what I said?
I've long since died!
Uh oh. What's going on?
--[screaming]
--[RUKO] Mayu!
Ruko...
Hold on!
[MAYU]
Why?
Why are you trying to
protect the LRIGs I created?
Back then, no one
ever tried to protect me.
No one held me
in their arms.
No one!
[RUKO] I'm sure if this
wasn't how things were,
if we'd somehow met before you
started the Selector Battles,
I would have really liked you.
And we would have been friends.
[MAYU] If we had,
could things have changed?
[MAYU] I thought if
I were to die here,
all alone and forgotten
by the outside world,
I wanted others to know...
...that in some
small way I existed,
and I wanted them to feel the
pain of the life I lived here.
Even if the only way
was through hatred.
[RUKO] But...
You can change all that!
You can make friends! Real ones!
And not through hatred
and hurting people, either!
Guess what color
card I selected, Ru?
[RUKO] Why do you
want me to do that?
[MAYU]
With Urith at Level 5,
she's able to control
all of the colors.
But you see, this move
can only be used once, however.
If you can guess which color
I selected, you win, Ru.
Get it wrong, and it's over.
[MAYU] This card is
the color of my heart.
[RUKO]
What is she trying to say?
Is it the color of black?
The hatred she embodied by Kuro?
Or is it the color of white?
The love embodied by Shiro?
[MAYU (MERGED)]
Beyond the wall of black,
beyond the wall of white,
there existed a world
full of countless shades.
[RUKO]
I understand.
[URITH]
Hurry it up, already!
How long are you gonna
make me hold back?
[MAYU]
So tell me, Ru.
What color is this card?
It's the same
as this world.
So the "color" is obvious.
There is none.
What?!
[URITH screaming]
[URITH]
W-Wait a second!
[screaming]
No, not this!
Mayu, please, you can't let me
be executed without a fight!
No!
[screaming]
[MAYU] I have nothing in
my hand, and no Arts to use.
Simply put, I can't do
anything in this turn at all.
Do you know why
I chose non-colored?
Because it's one that erases all
and marks the end of everything.
Maybe that's true.
But that also means that
it marks a new beginning.
And because of that, you can
color it any way you want.
[RUKO]
Paint the entire world.
Don't be afraid.
So you mean...
I can have a second chance?
[RUKO]
Yep.
[crying]
Then someone--Someone
will hold me and call my name?
Yes.
[MAYU crying]
Mayu...
[MAYU (MERGED)]
Ruko.
We need to act quickly.
Let's take our oath before
this world disappears.
But this time, let's make
your real wish come true.
Hang on. But my wish--
It was to turn the
girls who became LRIGs
back to their original selves.
Isn't that correct?
It's to turn the girls
who became LRIGs into humans.
[gasps]
Wait, just listen.
Once you've returned
to your original form,
then the Tama and Yuki
parts of you--
They might
actually become human.
[MAYU (MERGED)]
Ru, you're like a little kid.
You have to understand,
making a selection means
one thing, not everything.
I've made my selection.
I'm not going
to budge ever again.
I won't make one choice
at the sacrifice
of something
or someone else.
That's how I'll live.
Even if isn't easy and even
if it brings me pain and tears,
that's still better than giving
up halfway or compromising.
That's my final decision.
That's the selection
I've made, okay?
[MAYU (MERGED)]
As I said, just like a kid.
Oh, yeah?
You're one to talk, Mayu.
[RUKO, MAYU (MERGED)] "I accept
the laws of the Selector."
"And upon this sacred oath, a
new Eternal Girl shall be born!"
[HATSU] Look, dear, that
building's finally finished.
Guess the city didn't
disappear after all, huh?
Oh my.
Why are you so dressed up?
Do you have plans
with your friends?
Mmm-hmm!
We're studying
for the big exam.
[HATSU]
What about dinner?
[RUKO] I'll be back by then,
but in the meantime,
I've gotta run, Grandma. Bye!
[RUKO gasps]
--[RUKO] What the--?
--[AYUMU] Jeez.
Thanks a lot, Ru.
You'd think you'd be used to me
sleeping under here by now.
Y'know, there is a couch in here
you could sleep on
instead, weirdo.
[HATSU]
Be careful, out there.
[RUKO]
I will! See ya, Grandma!
You have a great day now.
[HATSU laughs]
If I didn't know any better, I'd
hardly recognize her anymore!
[AYUMU]
Guess so, huh?
[HATSU] That girl.
She's grown up so much.
[YUZUKI]
Aww!
That's it!
My brain can't take
any more of this!
[HITOE] Um, but we've only
been at it for an hour.
[RUKO]
She's right.
If you want to go the
same school as Hitoe,
you've gotta really
buckle down like her.
[YUZUKI]
Hitoe.
Just gimme some of your
big brain? Please?
[YUZUKI] Hey. How about
we take a break at least?
A break, huh?
[RUKO, YUZUKI, HITOE]
Let's play WIXOSS!
[YUZUKI]
Trash Rhino with Tawil!
[RUKO] Wow, the Activation
Ability on Yuzuki's new LRIG
is crazy powerful!
Kazuki recommended
I try some different cards
so I could learn
a few new tricks.
And while I've gotten
better overall, to be honest,
none of the new LRIGs match me
nearly as well as Hanayo did.
[RUKO] The world of the
Selector Battles has ended.
We're free.
[RUKO] All of the girls who
were sealed into cards as LRIGs
were able to return
to their former selves
and their former lives,
just like I had hoped.
The Selector Battles...
Sometimes I wonder if
those girls even remember
what the game was about.
A game that was born from the
hatred and sorrow of one girl.
Someone who never
knew love, only loneliness.
It was a game of broken rules.
One where sadness awaited you,
no matter what
selection you made.
But still...
A lucky few of us,
we were able to find
something within that world.
We found a way
around the rules,
a way to make our own selection.
The right one.
The funny thing is, if we
didn't participate in the game,
we never would have found out
what was really important to us.
But that's not
the end of the story.
Instead, it's a new beginning.
[RUKO] So even if there's
a long road ahead of me,
it's the one I've chosen.
[TAMA]
Ru...
Ru!
[RUKO] I know there's
a choice out there
that sacrifices nothing.
[RUKO] And I know I'm
going to find it somehow.
[RUKO] So I keep looking.
And that is my selection.