[KAZUKI] Attack with
Cannon. And end turn.
[BOY] Argh, dang,
Kazuki, you're good!
Okay, one more match!
I'm not gonna quit until
I win at least one of these!
'Kay, but you realize that
means you're never goin' home.
[BOY] Wise guy, eh?
Can't believe we finally
caught you without your sister.
Come on, you don't have
to say it like that.
[GIRL A] Hey, guys?
Can we play too?
We got decks and all,
but I dunno.
The rules are kind of
hard to understand.
[GIRL B] You're good
at this. Right, Kazuki?
[KAZUKI] Huh?
If you don't mind, could
you teach me a few tricks?
Oh, uh. Sure.
[RUKO] A WIXOSS party?
It's really just an excuse
for people to play together.
When we did these before,
it was all guys, but lately,
a bunch of girls your age
have been showing up too.
You three should come!
Oh come on, please?
Just sign up already!
Oh, and you should all
wear matching outfits!
That would be adorable!
I could help out, if you like!
[MAN'S VOICE] Momoka?
Huh?
You finally came by!
Oh, and you can still sign
up the day of the event,
so don't be afraid to
stop by and check it out.
Um... Cool.
So?
[MOMOKA giggles]
I'll be done in a few minutes.
Hang tight.
[MAN] Cool.
Yuzuki?
Sorry. What do you think?
Are we in, or what?
[IONA] Participating as a
Selector without having a wish
is more than just wrong.
It's blasphemy.
[YUZUKI] I'm going either way!
I might even find another
Selector to battle!
Yeah... But my wish already--
Right. It already came true.
Uh-huh.
So if I won, it wouldn't
be fair to the person I beat.
There's no need to
be greedy, after all.
But if the other player isn't
a Selector, it'll be fine.
Meaning we're free to fight
all the dudes we want.
Good point! As long as
nobody's dreams are at stake,
I'm definitely up
for a battle or two!
Yeah!
Sure. That sounds okay.
I suppose I'm on board.
If nothing else, it's a chance
to try out my new deck.
Right, Midoriko?
[HITOE gasps]
[HITOE] Midoriko?
Oh. Mm-hmm.
Okay! Sweet!
[HITOE &amp; RUKO giggle]
[YUZUKI] So, ladies, I was
thinking about Momoka's idea
for us to match our outfits.
We could be like a pop group!
Huh?
[HITOE] That's cute,
but... kinda pricey.
Yeah, we spent
too much on cards.
Oh well.
Oh! Hey, look!
[YUZUKI] Now that's more
in our price range!
It's not quite as fancy. But
we can still match with these!
Scrunchies, huh?
Mm-hmm! We might not
look much like a pop group.
But try it!
[HITOE gasps]
Well, you gotta go with
green to match your deck!
Ahh...
[HITOE giggles]
Oh, cool,
I found a red one.
Ruko's deck is white.
Huh... No luck.
You can take this
weird-looking one instead.
Don't give me
the icky one!
[YUZUKI] How's this?
[RUKO] You're picking
ugly ones on purpose!
Stop it!
[YUZUKI] Okay, sorry!
[HITOE] And then,
we all bought these
matching scrunchies!
That's lovely! And I'm thrilled
that you're making new friends.
But your hair is still
wet from your shower.
Your scrunchie is
going to mess it up.
It's fine! So, anyway.
Ruko almost got this
weird-looking one,
but she ended up
with aqua instead,
even though her
deck is white.
[HITOE'S MOTHER] All right, you
can tell me all about it later,
but first, go dry your hair,
and put something warmer on!
You're going to
catch your death.
[HITOE] Yes ma'am.
[MIDORIKO sighs]
Aw. It did get all messed up!
Yeep! And the
scrunchie's all damp, too!
Of course it is.
Ugh. I'm so stupid.
[MIDORIKO] Hitoe?
Yeah, what is it?
I think it's best
if you get rid of me.
Wha--! Get rid of you? Why?
[MIDORIKO] Your wish
already came true.
There's no need for
you to battle anymore.
Sure. But who
cares about that?
I like you a whole
bunch, Midoriko.
I would never want
to get rid of you!
I'm afraid that if you keep me,
something might happen.
Something terrible.
[HITOE] So what?
[MIDORIKO gasps]
[HITOE] Before I even met Ruko
and Yuzuki, you were my friend,
Midoriko, and nothing
will change that!
Oh, Hitoe...
[HITOE] I don't want to hear
you talk like that ever again!
Oh yeah. Still need
to dry my hair.
[YUZUKI grunts softly]
Aw! I suck.
[KAZUKI] Something wrong?
Not really.
I just can't get my hair
tied up right, that's all.
You are kind of clumsy
with that stuff.
Here, let me get it for you.
Huh?
No, it's fine! Really!
[KAZUKI] Don't freak out.
[YUZUKI] I'm not freaking out!
I just need to learn!
[RUKO] It's cold!
Oh. Here, look! There's a
big giraffe on the building!
Cool! Is it gonna
battle the other giraffe?
Tama. Not everything is
about battles, you know?
I am right.
So battle me.
[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO] Iona was
really pretty, but, uh,
she was also kind of scary.
Don't you think?
Tama can beat
all the scaries!
[RUKO chuckles]
[turnstile beeps]
[HITOE] Looks like
I'm here a bit early.
I made it to the
meeting spot...
I'll be waiting...
And send.
[HITOE] It's funny,
but when I'm standing
in a big crowd like this. I
almost feel like a normal girl.
[MIDORIKO] Come on, Hitoe,
you are a normal girl.
I'll take your
word for it.
It's nice out.
[HITOE] When I first moved
to Tokyo, somehow, I felt like
there wasn't a sky here.
Thanks to all the
skyscrapers and stuff.
But there it is, as bright
and blue as it's ever been.
All this time, I never
noticed. How sad.
I just needed to look up.
Hitoe...
[MIDORIKO gasps]
Drop me! Throw me away now!
Please! Hurry!
Huh?
[train doors ding]
[YUZUKI] Ruko! Let's go!
[RUKO] I'm sorry!
There were a whole bunch
of people in the bathroom
and the kid behind me was
about to go in her pants,
so I let her cut in line.
[YUZUKI] We're making
Hitoe wait!
Okay, okay!
[YUZUKI] Huh. She
said she'd be here.
Too short! I can't see!
Guessing you came
up empty too?
Uh-huh.
[YUZUKI] She isn't answering
my texts, either.
Maybe she got mad at us
because we were late.
She wouldn't lose her temper
over something like that.
Right? Back me up
on this, Hanayo.
[YUZUKI] Hanayo?
Oh. Yeah, of course.
[TAMA] Field!
[HANAYO gasps]
Somethin' goin' on, Tama?
There's a battlefield
somewhere! Close!
What?! Around here?
--Not Hitoe...?
--[HITOE gasps]
[HITOE] They're strong.
Really strong!
[MIDORIKO screams]
Midoriko! I'm sorry!
No. Don't worry about me.
But it's my fault
you're suffering!
I'll try to end this
quickly, okay?
I don't need to win,
I'll lose on purpose.
Please! You have
to keep fighting!
You can't give up!
It's fine. Really. The only
wish I wanted already came true.
And now, neither one
of us have to go through
these painful battles anymore!
Hitoe. Listen.
Huh?
There's something important
I haven't told you.
What do you mean?
You know all about winning
and becoming an Eternal Girl.
Your wish.
[YUZUKI] Hitoe?
Where did you go?
[YUZUKI grunts]
--Sorry, mister!
--[YUZUKI] Hitoe!
However, you don't know
what it means to lose.
[CROWD chattering]
[RUKO &amp; YUZUKI panting]
Tama. We close?
[TAMA] Hmm...
The battlefield
went bye-bye.
[RUKO gasps]
Hey, Hanayo, do you
know anything about this?
Hey. Look!
[BOTH] Hitoe!
[YUZUKI] There you are!
You had us all worried!
[YUZUKI] Hitoe, what's wrong?
[HITOE gasps]
Wha-What do you want?
How do you know my name?
If this is a joke,
I don't get it.
Hey! Wait!
[HITOE screams]
What the--?!
--[HITOE whimpers]
--[YUZUKI] Are you okay?
[RUKO] Hitoe. Tell
us what's wrong.
[HITOE screams]
[HANAYO] Stand back!
Don't touch her!
Whoever you are,
leave me alone!
I...
[TAMA] Hitoe... lost.
[RUKO] What?
Tama is not sensing
her Selector power.
She had a battle and lost.
No...
Are you saying she's
not a Selector anymore?
Did something messed
up happen to her
'cause she lost
her third battle?
What is this?
[YUZUKI] Hanayo!
After three losses, your
status as a Selector is revoked.
As for your wish,
it becomes corrupted.
[RUKO gasps]
[YUZUKI] You mean like
you get a curse?
[HANAYO] Yes.
For example, let's say your
wish was to become wealthy.
After losing three battles,
not only would that wish
fail to come true, you
would plummet into poverty.
[HANAYO] If your wish was
to be an expert pianist,
you wouldn't just lose your
piano. Something would happen
that would prevent you
from playing ever again.
Something to ensure your
wish could never come true.
That's awful.
I'm not really getting this.
So, what happened to Hitoe?
All I can tell you is her
wish was to "make friends".
You can imagine what a
corruption of that would be.
So, you're saying
she lost her friends?
[HANAYO sighs]
Far worse than that.
She can never make
friends again.
You saw what
state she was in.
Seems if anyone has even the
potential to be her friend,
her body goes through
some sort of violent shock
when they try to approach her.
No way!
[HANAYO] Horrible, but
unfortunately, there's more.
With her third loss, not only
is her Selector status gone,
so are all her memories
related to those battles,
as if they never
even took place.
[HITOE] What is this?
What's happening? I'm scared!
[YUZUKI] Hitoe, what's wrong?
[HITOE] How did they
know me? Who were they?
[HITOE grunts]
[HITOE] That didn't hurt me.
[HITOE] Why...?
[HITOE grunts]
[HITOE] Oh, God! Why?!
Why does this hurt?
I can't! No! It hurts
just thinking about them!
Make it stop!
That's it!
I'll win and wish for Hitoe
to go back to normal!
I finally have a dream
worth fighting for!
I didn't think of that! Right!
[HANAYO] It won't work.
[BOTH] Huh?
Even though it didn't happen
as a result of winning battles,
her wish did come true.
The corruption cannot be undone
by another Selector's wish.
What the hell?!
That's kind of an important
detail you decided to keep
secret from me!
Damn it, why won't
you say something?!
Hanayo!
[YUZUKI whimpers]
[YUZUKI sobs]
[BOTH cry]
[MIDORIKO sighs]
Yeah the sky would
get cloudy, wouldn't it?
Looks like rain soon, too.
I know I don't have
any right to cry.
After ruining such
an innocent wish,
any fate I face
will be too kind.
I really did care
for you, Hitoe.
And yet, after this,
I wish that we had
never even met each other.
[MIDORIKO sobs]
Goodbye...
[YUZUKI cries softly]
[YUZUKI] I trusted you
all this time, Hanayo.
I don't know what to do.
I'm afraid of you!
You can get rid of me.
[HANAYO] It'll be easy.
Just throw me away.
That's not funny!
[knock on door]
[KAZUKI] Yuzuki?
Something wrong?
It's nothing, I'm okay.
[KAZUKI] Were you
fighting with Hanayo?
[YUZUKI grunts]
I didn't wanna say it, but
you've been acting weird lately.
[YUZUKI] Huh...?
You used to talk to
me about everything,
whether it was good or bad.
[YUZUKI] Not everything...
[KAZUKI] If something's
bothering you, then tell me.
I'm here for you.
[YUZUKI] You wouldn't say
that if you knew the truth.
[KAZUKI] I mean, we've been
together our whole lives.
[YUZUKI] What if
I just told him?
[KAZUKI] Yuzuki?
Really, I'm fine.
Don't worry about me!
I see... You don't
want to tell me.
Huh?
Okay. If you don't
need me, it's fine.
Kazuki, I--
[phone rings]
[KAZUKI] Hello? Oh, hey.
Real good, thanks.
Tomorrow, huh?
And everyone is coming?
No, that should be okay, but--
No, I'll be there. Sounds good.
Yeah. See ya.
[YUZUKI] I hate this.
I hate this so much...
This is really neat!
We've never been here before!
I guess not. I usually only
come to sit-down restaurants
like this with
Grandma.
[TAMA] You're not going home?
No, I can't. Not yet. Whenever I
fail a test or hide something
from Grandma, she
knows right away.
Ru...
[RUKO] Tama, did you know?
Nuh-uh. I don't know anything.
Everything's all fuzzy
and white in Tama's head,
so I can't think at all.
But I, I love battles!
I know that much!
And I want more!
And I don't like Ru sad...
I don't want that.
Tama.
[AKIRA] I found you!
Piriluk said a battle
happened around here,
so I came to check it out.
I figured it might be
Yuzu-poo and the gals,
so I sent a text
to her and Hitoe,
to see what was
up, you know?
Yuzu-poo was too mean to reply,
but Hitoe... Ha, ha. Well, look.
It's like she didn't even
know who I was anymore!
Guess she lost her third match
and got kicked to the curb, huh?
You've known all along
what happens to Selectors
and you never told anyone?!
--What the heck?
--Kids today...
[AKIRA] C'mere.
[AKIRA] ♪ Let's have
a potty party! ♪
Uhm... What are you...?
[AKIRA] So funny story,
the first time I saw
a Selector battle, it wasn't
even mine. It was Iona's.
[RUKO] Huh?
[AKIRA] On my way out from a
photo shoot, I guess she was
picking a fight with
some other Selector.
'Cause I got pulled into
their field out of the blue.
She could have warned me, right?
[AKIRA] Anyhoo, her opponent
had already lost two battles
and was at the
end of her rope.
She was all like, huffing
and puffing and just,
super-sick looking.
I could tell she wanted
to win real bad though.
[AKIRA] Well, Iona
didn't give a crap.
Long story short, there
was a lot of thrashing,
and not much in the
way of happy endings.
[AKIRA] When it was over,
she must've had a stroke
or something. It was bad.
Like, ambulance and everything.
I don't know if you heard, but
Iona's LRIG is super sadistic.
That poor girl didn't
stand a chance.
[RUKO] D-do you know
what happened to her?
None of my business, really.
I mean, I saw that she got
taken to the hospital.
But she was looking pretty bad,
so it's tough to say.
[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO] No, that's terrible...
I know, like,
for serious!
Compared to something like that.
Heh, not being able to make
friends isn't so bad, right?
H-how did you know?
You forgot already? When we
fought, I did that awesome thing
where I could
see her wish?
Well, she wasn't exactly
Miss Popularity to begin with.
So, who cares?
This is kind of a
plus for you, really.
Now you don't have to humor
the poor disaster anymore.
Hanging around her wasn't
doing you any favors.
I mean, seriously,
she was super frumpy.
At least now she knows
nobody will be her friend,
so she doesn't have to latch
onto people like a parasite.
So yeah. Even if she
doesn't make friends,
it's pretty much better
for everyone that way.
That's really what
you think, huh?
Huh?!
Yeah, of course.
So anyhow I--
You take that back!
Not gonna do it!
[RUKO growls]
Listen up! You take it back,
or I will never forgive you!
Wow. I am, like,
really scared.
You must think super
highly of yourself, huh?
"I can't live if Ru-Ru
won't forgive me!"
You know, if you
truly can't forgive me,
why don't we have a battle?
I mean, if you
beat me bad enough,
maybe I'll cry and see the
error of my wicked old ways!
[RUKO] Yeah, fine.
[TAMA] Ru?
[RUKO] We can battle.
And after I beat you,
we're going to visit Hitoe.
So you can tell my friend
that you're sorry!
[RUKO] Hitoe lost three times.
[AKIRA] That is, like,
so messed up!
[YUZUKI] Do you
think I'm stupid?
[RUKO] No! No, please!
[YUZUKI] What's
it matter to you?
[RUKO] Next time:
"This Pure Heart."