[KAZUKI] What?! You were
playing WIXOSS until four AM?
[RUKO] Yeah, I showed it to
my Grandma, and she got hooked.
The deal was, loser had to
peel tangerines, and I lost.
Now my hands are
all orange. Look!
[YUZUKI] Ewww!
--[RUKO yawns]
--[YUZUKI] Yeesh.
There's this stuff
called "soap"?
Yeah, thanks.
So you were saying we don't need
to battle each other anymore?
Yeah. The world can make
room for one more Eternal Girl.
Both of us can have
our wishes come true!
But... I don't have one.
I haven't even thought about it.
C'mon!
--[KAZUKI] Let's go!
--Hey, wait up, you guys!
Finding other Selectors
is a real pain in the butt,
not to mention exhausting.
You mean there
aren't too many?
No. Or at least it
seems like that,
since there's no
easy way to find 'em.
Right? Tell 'er, Hanayo.
Yes. But LRIGs are
attracted to each other.
We can identify
Selectors on sight.
Right over there for example.
Huh?
[YUZUKI] Iona Urazoe.
What about her?
Is she a Selector?
She's on TV a lot. Even
had a new single jus' drop.
[HANAYO] The girl next
to her is one, too.
[YUZUKI] Really? She's in
magazines a lot too, it's...
Oh, come on. It's
on the tip of my tongue.
[GIRL A] Akira!
That's her!
Uh...
Ah?
Hey, look it says here
she goes to Gochu High!
[YUZUKI gasps]
Wait! Which high
school? Say it again?
Uh... What...?
[students murmuring]
--Uh...
--Huh?
[RUKO] Maybe this
isn't the best time.
[YUZUKI] C'mon, better
now than never!
But I get first
dibs, okay?
I'll set up matches for
after-school and--
Aah!
It's her! Akira!
[RUKO] Wow!
Just like the pictures...
She's so pretty.
Now's our chance!
Let's go challenge her!
[GIRL] Wait! Akira, please!
I'm begging you!
You have to battle me!
[ALL] Huh?!
That girl is...
...a Selector?!
[GIRL gasps]
You're... Selectors too?
Who are these
losers?
Akira's too busy to sign
autographs right now.
So buzz off!
Uhh! No. Wait. I just want--
[AKIRA laughs]
[gasps]
Thanks for being my fan!
[GIRL gasps]
[AKIRA] If you want
something autographed,
then let's go someplace
private! You guys, too!
Wha--? Us?
[YUZUKI] C'mon, Ruko!
Akira's too
nice to her fans.
[AKIRA] Here! Perfect!
[AKIRA] All right!
With all these
Selectors, I'm so lucky!
Or as I like to
say: "Aki-lucky"!
Um... I don't--
So let's get a battle done
before class starts, okay?
Which one of you
girls is up first?
[GIRL] I-I am.
[AKIRA] All righty then.
What's your name?
Ahh! My name is Hitoe.
Love it! Now let's get
this party started, yo!
One nice and friendly
battle ready to: Open!
[HITOE gasps]
[RUKO gasps]
[BOTH grunting]
Ah...
[HITOE whimpers softly]
[HANAYO] I assume you
both are wondering
what you're doing here.
When a battlefield is
opened, any Eternal Girl
candidates nearby
are drawn inside.
Well that's lame!
--[TAMA meowing]
--Wait! That sounds like...!
--[TAMA squeals]
--Tama!
Hey! You're gonna get
my hair all goofed up
if you keep doing that!
Look, it's starting!
I'm first. Guess
it's now or never!
Let's go: Battle Start!
Are you ready, Midoriko?
Yeah. Leave it to me!
My LRIG is
Aki-lucky, too!
Meet Piriluk! Go
stompy-stompy on them, okay?
Understood.
[HANAYO] A green deck
versus a blue deck, huh?
There's a possibility
this Hitoe girl may have
the upper hand.
Draw! Energy charge,
Midoriko! Now Grow!
First up: Summon Sparrow!
Sparrow! Attack!
[MIDORIKO grunts]
[AKIRA] Whoa! She's
starting off strong!
[PIRILUK grunts]
It worked?
All I have to do is
keep Midoriko growing
so we don't
lose momentum!
Ooh, what a meanie!
Whatever shall we do?
You got this, Piriluk, just
Grow and we'll take her out.
[AKIRA] But those green
decks really are unnerving!
There's no telling what
cards Little Miss Four-Eyes
has in her hand!
To make things less scary...
I think I'll just have her
throw one of those cards away.
[HITOE gasps]
[AKIRA] All right, Hitoe, I'm
gonna choose one of your cards
at random. Hope it's one you
can afford to play without!
Spell: Too Bad!
'Kay, not looking. Oh yeah!
I'm bettin' that's a
Level 3 card, isn't it?
Expose.
[HITOE gasps]
[AKIRA] Bullseye!
Aki-lucky guess!
The card just vanished!
It's one of the blue
deck's top strategies.
A player can force their
opponent to lose a card.
That sucks.
[AKIRA] Piriluk, Grow!
And while you're at it,
freeze Hitoe's Sparrow!
Clip its wings!
[HITOE gasps]
[AKIRA] Aww, your cute little
birdy's been put on ice
'til the next turn!
No. Midoriko...
What should I do?
I only have two cards
left! If I mess up...
[HITOE sobs]
Just calm
down, Hitoe!
If that's already
gotcha freakin' out,
wait 'til you see the other
stuff I've got in store!
Go, Piriluk.
Arts. Peeping Analyze.
[HITOE screams]
[AKIRA] Seen this
one? Super handy.
I pick a level,
then you throw away
all your cards that match it.
All... my cards...?
I wonder what
I should pick?
Let's see... Level... two?
[HITOE whimpers]
This is bad!
She can read her!
[AKIRA] Three?
Four...?
[HITOE gasps]
Yeah, that's the one.
All Level Four cards:
Go buh-bye!
[HITOE screams]
[HITOE gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[HITOE sobs]
[AKIRA laughs]
[AKIRA] Jeez,
pull it together!
[AKIRA sighs]
[AKIRA] Not that you
have any hope of winning,
but now you got me
wondering why
you want to become
an Eternal Girl.
Let's find out your
little wish, shall we?
Ah...
[PIRILUK] The poor thing.
[PIRILUK] She has no friends.
[HITOE gasps]
[AKIRA cackles]
Aw, nobody wuvs Hitoe!
--[MIDORIKO] Hitoe! Come on!
--She doesn't have any fwiends!
We're still in this, so ignore
her and don't give up!
--[HITOE sobs quietly]
--[AKIRA] Loser!
Screw this!
Yuzuki, what--?!
I'm gonna put a stop
to her right now!
I know! I'll interfere
just like Kazuki did
when you and I
had our battle!
That should do the trick!
[HANAYO] It won't.
Why not?
Kazuki didn't stop the
battle the last time,
it was the teacher.
And that was only because
of an irregular occurrence.
An interruption by someone who
knew nothing about the cards.
Also... if ever a battle
is stopped on purpose,
a huge penalty
is issued.
A penalty?
What about one for the way
Akira's been playing?
She hasn't broken
any rules thus far.
Yeah, but--!
Dang. This game...
it's horrible...
[RUKO] How could she...?
[TAMA yells]
[RUKO gasps]
[TAMA meowing]
Tama.
Yeah, Piriluk?
Finish this.
Hitoe!
I... don't have any
Life Cloth left.
You can't give
up now!
Take guard against
the attack!
Why? I'm just gonna lose
anyway. What's the use?
[MIDORIKO] Believe
in me! Please!
Hitoe...
[MIDORIKO gasps]
[MIDORIKO screams]
[HITOE gasps]
[HITOE whimpers]
Midoriko!
[HANAYO] The game's over.
Akira won.
[RUKO gasps]
Hmph.
[HITOE] I'm sorry.
I tried, but... I can't.
Midoriko begged me to
fight, but I gave up.
And now she's the
one paying for it.
It's all my fault!
Um... You okay?
[HITOE sobs]
[RUKO] Hitoe!
So. Who wants
to battle next?
Oh! Already, Piriluk?
Crud. She falls
asleep so quickly.
Well, then. We'll just
have to battle tomorrow!
Okay? Can I get
your cell number?
Well, you see... I
don't have a cell phone...
No way, that is
so old school!
What's yours?
I, um...
Yuzuki.
Gotta go! We're super
late for class!
[KAZUKI &amp; YUZUKI gasp]
[AKIRA] I am not letting you go
until you give up the digits.
Right now.
[YUZUKI gasps]
[school bells chiming]
[YUZUKI] Ruko!
Ah.
D'ja get in trouble
for being tardy?
[RUKO] Yeah. But I just had
to stand out in the hall.
It was math class so
I was lucky, or, sorry,
I mean, "Aki-lucky"!
[YUZUKI] Oh God, make me cringe.
Damn. Akira's a monster.
She'd probably thrash me as
hard as that other girl.
Well, why did you give her
your phone number then?
What choice did I have?!
She wasn't gonna let us go!
Oh. Hey, I could battle
Akira if you want me to.
[HANAYO] Don't worry.
As long as you don't agree
to a battle, you'll be fine.
[YUZUKI] Yeah, good point.
I was watching from the
outside. And you're right.
She's strong.
[YUZUKI] Yeah, but that Hitoe
girl wasn't bad either.
I didn't know all the
Eternal Girl candidates
would be this tough.
I wonder... if I
can win at all.
Sure you can! I mean, all you
need to do is update your deck.
But that means we'd have
to go to the card shop.
Umm... Yeah, unless
that's a problem?
Uh. No.
Ooh, I've never been
to one before! Can I go?
Sure, we'll all
go together.
[RUKO] Cool!
[RUKO] Whoa. I never knew
there was a card shop
in this neighborhood.
So, Kazuki, you're really
an expert on all this stuff,
aren't you?
Yeah. I was playing WIXOSS
before it got popular
with everyone else.
When I recommended it to Yuzuki,
her deck had Hanayo in it.
Right, Yuzuki?
[YUZUKI gasps]
[YUZUKI] Uh... Right!
Well, we're here.
It's so big!
[RUKO] Wow. This place takes
cards pretty seriously.
Huuuh...
[SHOP KEEP] Hey! Kazuki!
We just got a new
WIXOSS set in today!
And Yuzuki tagged
along too! Been awhile.
Yeah... Guess so.
We're hoping to update
Yuzuki's deck today.
Would you mind giving
us some advice?
'Course not! You know I'd do
anything for you, Kazuki!
Just tell me what you
need and I'm all yours!
[YUZUKI groans softly]
[SHOP KEEP] Let's see, Yuzuki's
deck is Red Ambition, so...
In my opinion, it should cycle a
lot better with an Adamasphere.
Oh, yeah, I think I've
heard of that one.
It's a SIGNI from the
new series, right?
[SHOP KEEP] Yep.
But there's aren't any singles
on the collector's market yet.
[KAZUKI grunts]
[KAZUKI sighs]
All these packs
and nothin'.
What about these cards?
Nah. They won't really mesh well
with the rest of Yuzuki's deck.
[RUKO gasps]
Well, if you don't want
this one, do you think
I could have it then?
Huh?
[RUKO] Well, tell me
if I'm doing this wrong,
but it looks like if I use
this little buddy in my deck,
I can search
non-colored SIGNIs.
Oh yeah! You sure can!
I'm surprised you know that!
For a newbie, you're good!
[RUKO chuckles sheepishly]
[KAZUKI] Guess we'll
have to wait for someone
to sell a single.
For now, you'll just have to get
better with the deck you have.
All right, it's your turn.
I'll draw this
one and charge...
And now "Grow".
[KAZUKI] Hey, wait a minute.
Show me your hand.
[YUZUKI gasps]
Level 2 again?
Y'know, you'd probably do better
if you strategize your growing.
Uh... Yeah, but--
[KAZUKI] You have to.
Your gameplay is way
too straightforward.
[YUZUKI gasps]
[YUZUKI] What's wrong with
being straightforward?!
I... I'm, uh...
I'm goin' to bed!
Yuzuki...
[YUZUKI panting]
[YUZUKI sighs]
[YOUNG YUZUKI] I'm gonna
marry Kazuki one day!
[PRESCHOOL TEACHER]
Aww, how cute!
[YOUNG YUZUKI giggles]
[PRESCHOOL GIRL]
Ewww, that's icky!
Yeah, brothers and sisters can't
get married, you dumb baby!
Huh...?
If you want to, then there's
something's wrong with you!
You're a weirdo!
I'm a weirdo?
Yuzuki!
[YUZUKI]
"Too straightforward"...
What's wrong with that? It just
means I'm honest, doesn't it?
How exactly is that supposed
to be a bad thing?
[cell phone rings]
[YUZUKI gasps]
[YUZUKI] Akira...
"So, who's gonna
battle me tomorrow?
Yuzu-poo? Or Ru-ru?"
[YUZUKI] I can't lose
to her. And I won't.
[TAMA meows]
Wait there, Tama, okay?
[TAMA mewls sadly]
[RUKO] I feel really
sorry for that Hitoe girl.
Meow?
[RUKO] But still...
It's funny. But I... I feel like
I have to battle Akira myself,
even if I know
I can't win.
[RUKO gasps]
[TAMA groans sadly]
No! I was just
thinking out loud!
I don't even have a wish,
so why would I get into
a battle with her?
Do battle!
[TAMA whimpers]
I can't think of anything
that I'd even wish for.
'Cept Grandma living
a long time.
That's a wish, right?
[TAMA meows sadly]
[school bells chiming]
[cell phone rings]
Ah.
[RUKO] Oh, hey.
You're not hanging
with Kazuki today?
[YUZUKI] No, he had
something to do.
Oh yeah, like what?
[cell phone rings]
That's your phone.
Of course.
Geez, Akira,
obsessed much?
Ahh... Um.
This last text says she's on
her way here now to find us!
[YUZUKI gasps]
Oh my gosh, Ru. Let's
find some place to hide!
[RUKO] Yeah, right.
But where?
[YUZUKI] Hey! Let's go in here.
Karaoke?
Yeah, they've got private
rooms where Akira won't
be able to find us.
I've never done
karaoke before.
Like, what songs
should I even sing?
Figure it out when
we get inside!
[RUKO] No, wait
a minute, hang on!
You gotta plan these
things out first!
Y'know, like strategize
for the big fight!
Strategize?
Mm-hmm! Yeah, 'cause--
Ah.
Ah? Kazuki...
[RUKO] That's the girl
who works at the card shop.
Um...
Momoka. Isn't it?
[YUZUKI gasps]
[RUKO] Wow, they look pretty
cozy together, don't they?
Hey! Maybe they're
on a da--!
[YUZUKI] Shut up!
[RUKO gasps]
Wha...? Is something wrong?
You know what?
I don't get you.
Maybe it's 'cause
you don't have a wish.
After that battle
the other day...
you saw what's at stake and how
people like Hitoe can get hurt.
Are you taking this seriously?!
Yes! Of course I am!
Don't think like that!
Why not?
'Cause I have no idea
what you're thinking, Ruko!
[YUZUKI cries]
Yeah, well. That
makes two of us.
But... I wish I knew.
That'd be nice...
[HITOE] Please. I'm begging you.
For Midoriko's
sake, please!
[RUKO gasps]
Have a battle with
me! You have to!
Me?
[AKIRA] There you are!
Goodness. Have you been hiding
from me, you naughty girl?
Guess I'm just lucky I found ya.
Aki-lucky!
[YUZUKI] Hey, Akira.
[AKIRA] Come on down here! This
battle will be flippin' epic!
We are gonna have so much
fun! But I'll have more.
'Cause I'm gonna beat the
living crap out of you.
[YUZUKI] Bring it.
I've got some stress
I need to work off.
[RUKO] I shouldn't
win. It's wrong.
[AKIRA] Piriluk! Go: Peek-a-Boo!
[RUKO] Hold on. Did you...?
[YUZUKI] Open!
[RUKO] We've even got
a nice breeze, huh?
[RUKO] Next time:
"This Nonsensical Peace."