A... ki... ra...
[MILULUN]
Jeez, Aki-lovely!
That was nasty!
Milulun's so scared!
[AKIRA]
I have to... keep doing them...
Huh?
[AKIRA]
Selector battles.
Oh?
And what's your wish?
Urith's scar,
I want it to heal...
[AKIRA]
...as quickly as possible.
Hmph.
Well, it will if you're lucky!
That's right, Aki-lucky.
[RUKO]
Are you all right, Hitoe?
You didn't get hurt, did you?
Oh, no, I'm fine, thanks.
I'm just a little
shaken up, that's all.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
No, wait. I need to
apologize to you.
You had to suffer
through a battle for me.
Yeah, but--
Plus, Iona had to relive
all those painful memories.
[gasps]
I don't deserve your sympathy.
[RUKO, HITOE]
Huh?
Both Shiro and I were
made by and from Mayu.
So then, in essence,
we're the ones who
created the Selector battles.
But that's Mayu's
fault, not yours--
You girls have every right to
hate us for what we've done!
And yet, you've still tried
to save all three of us.
[HITOE] I don't condone
what Mayu's done, but,
I do understand
where's she coming from.
Before now, I didn't have any
friends either; I was all alone.
I know how painful that is...
[gasps]
Every single time
I left the house,
I saw so many happy people
walking and talking
with their friends.
That just made me feel like
I was the loneliest person
in the entire world.
After hearing what Iona told
us about Mayu's history,
the loneliness that
I felt was nothing
compared to the sorts of things
she's had to go through...
Poor thing.
So, then...
Maybe that's it, guys.
Maybe what's it?
Mayu's wish.
Her real one, I think.
You mean it isn't... revenge?
[YUZUKI] Well, it always
felt kind of weird to me.
Why did Mayu make the rules
to the Selector
battles the way she did?
The girl who wins has
their wish taken away
and is sealed into a card?
That's a really
horrible thing and all,
but as far as revenge goes,
it doesn't make much sense.
I mean...
Things aren't as bad when
we're talking like we are now,
but more than anything else,
being in a card is... lonely.
It's a crushing... emptiness.
[YUZUKI]
So maybe Mayu's real wish,
It isn't revenge,
but wanting everyone to
know what it feels
like to be lonely.
To feel what she's been through.
[gasps]
[RUKO, HITOE]
Yuzuki...
I'm sorry!
I had no idea you felt that way!
So from now on, I'm going
to keep you close to me,
--even when I'm sleeping, okay?
--[YUZUKI] I'm fine! Thanks,
but come on, this is
mostly just weird!
Iona...
[IONA]
Unbelievable.
[RUKO]
What?
[IONA] With everything horrible
that she's put you through,
I find it rather surprising that
you're still looking
at Mayu with sympathy.
[RUKO]
Well, that's not entirely true.
But if you ask me,
I think the reason we
feel the way we do
is 'cause of how we
feel for you and Tama.
[RUKO]
I mean, you told us that
you and she were created
by and from Mayu, right?
Well, if that's the case, then
Mayu can't be all bad, can she?
[IONA]
You really think so?
Yeah, and you know what?
Since you guys became friends
with us, I bet Mayu could, too.
We just have to
convince her to listen,
and I think we can do that
by speaking from our hearts.
[IONA]
Yeah, but, my heart aches.
It must be because I
shouldn't feel this way...
Because I'm the Girl of Black.
But even though
this feeling hurts...
...it's so warm.
All I want to do is
keep embracing it.
What, why?
It's all wrong!
What's going on?
Why isn't Kuro the same anymore?
Selector battles need both--
Bright light on one side, and
shrouded darkness on the other.
If Kuro's going to
be this useless,
then she leaves me
no other choice.
We'll burn her card to ashes.
Won't we, Shiro?
[URITH (I)]
I can't believe this pampering.
A private hospital room
for this measly scratch?
That's the Urazoe
family for you.
[TAMA]
Um, are you okay, Urith?
Yes, it's a minor
wound, that's all.
[URITH (I)] Say, mind
if I ask you something?
Huh?
[URITH (I)]
Iona passed through many hands
as both a LRIG and a Selector
after Mayu created her
as the Girl of Black.
But where were you before
you ended up as Ruko's LRIG?
To be honest... Well, all I
seem to remember is meeting Ru.
I forgot about Mayu and Kuro
and everything else that
happened before that.
Even though I didn't have
any memory of my past...
It didn't matter because
I had Ru in my life.
I felt like I was born
just to meet her.
Oh.
Now, I know why Mayu did it.
Huh?
She got rid of you
and sent you here
because you're vomit-inducing.
[gasps]
[URITH (I)] She must have
gotten sick of your sweet,
little sunny spirit, clinging
like gunk to her heart.
She couldn't take any more,
so it was "so long, Shiro."
I bet you anything that's why
she put you in
Ruko's hands first.
Ruko is one horrifying girl.
After all, she can
destroy everything.
[whimpers]
[ELDORA]
So, Chiyori? What's next?
What do you mean?
"Even if I know the truth
behind the battles,
I'm never giving up my dream!
Hoo-yeah, onto the
next big battle!"
[ELDORA] That's you in
a nutshell, isn't it?
Such incredible evil.
Huh?
[CHIYORI]
There's no two ways about it.
How else could you describe
Selector battles?
Win or lose, only a
tragic ending awaits!
To suggest I jump into one
is real messed up and mean!
What are you, the
villain of a story
who wants to see me suffer?
Heh-heh. I gotta admit,
that would be amusing.
--[CHIYORI growls]
--[ELDORA grunts]
Just kidding, but
remember what you said.
Your wish is to enter
the world of the cards.
Or did you change
your mind already?
[CHIYORI]
Huh?
[ELDORA]
Guess that answers that.
[CHIYORI]
Yeah, you're right.
But if I lose one more time,
I'll be out of the game
and you won't be
my LRIG anymore.
[ELDORA] Well, sure, but
there's no use dwelling on it.
We'll jump off that bridge
when we come to it.
Yeah, I guess so.
Hey, on the subject of battles,
you were a human once
too, right, Eldora?
What was your wish back then?
Huh?
Well, uh... I forgot.
[CHIYORI]
Liar!
What? I just don't
wanna tell you!
Treat it like one of those
plot twists you like.
Why, you!
Don't get all worked up.
Really.
Besides, my wish totally
wasn't anything special.
I was pretty into it,
like you are, though.
[CHIYORI]
Uhh...
[HITOE]
Well, in any case,
I guess we need to speak
with Tama then, don't we?
[RUKO]
Yeah, but...
Are you okay with that?
It means seeing Urith.
[YUZUKI]
Good point.
Ruko and I can go without you.
It's okay. I appreciate
the concern, but I--
[phone rings, buzzes]
[RUKO, HITOE gasp]
[YUZUKI]
Maybe it's Urith!
[RUKO, HITOE gasp]
[hands clap]
[CHIYORI]
Please battle me!
[RUKO, HITOE]
Uh...
[CHIYORI]
It doesn't matter which one
of you guys I face either!
Just battle me, please!
Hey, get a hold of yourself!
If you lose one more time,
don't you know what'll happen?
Justice will prevail!
You're justice. Does make
us the evil ones?
[YUZUKI] Geez, you mean
you still don't get it,
even after what Fumio told us?
[AKIRA]
If they won't battle...
[RUKO, HITOE gasp]
[AKIRA]
...how's about doing it with me?
What are you waiting for?
Let's start the party.
Uh-oh! My Selector
Sense detects a villain!
[RUKO]
Wh-- Akira?
[ELDORA]
Cool. We'll fight.
[CHIYORI]
Huh?
[ELDORA]
Let's take this chick on.
Hey! I'm the Selector!
That's my call to make, not
yours, so pipe down, okay?
Why?
Oh wait, you're not
scared of losing, are you?
[growls] No, I'm not
scared of anything!
Let's do it, scar-face!
Chorizo's gonna mop
the floor with you and
end your wicked schemes!
No, don't!
[YUZUKI]
Wait, Chiyori, stop!
[RUKO]
Enough!
[CHIYORI yelling]
[AKIRA]
Hey!
You better get back here!
Lousy bitches!
[phone buzzes]
[gasps]
[GROUP panting]
[HITOE]
Ruko.
You don't think Akira's
going to chase us, do you?
[CHIYORI]
What gives?!
Are you two mental?!
Why did you guys
screw up my battle?
Because--
[YUZUKI]
If you really want to battle,
then we're not gonna stop you,
but be more selective
about who you fight, okay?
[ELDORA] Whatever. It
doesn't matter who we face.
[RUKO]
What?
That's right!
'Cause no matter who I square
off against, I'm gonna win!
[ELDORA laughs]
Pretty bold from someone
who's lost twice already!
[CHIYORI growls]
Yeah?!
Well, I can't wait to
win so I can get rid of
your snarky, back-talking
butt forever!
[ELDORA] Like having you
as a Selector is a picnic?
--Puh-leeze!
--[CHIYORI] What?!
Why, you little creep!
[HITOE]
I'll do it. I'll battle Chiyori.
--No!
--[YUZUKI] Huh?!
She's lost twice already
now, so her wish...
Don't you know what'll
happen if you beat her?
It'll be corrupted.
Hitoe...
It's all right Ruko.
I'm doing this, because
Chiyori is only one loss away.
What?
[YUZUKI] Wait, don't tell
me you're gonna let her win.
[HITOE]
No.
You see, right before
I had my third loss
and my wish got reversed,
Midoriko said this to me.
Drop me!
[HITOE gasps]
Throw me away, now!
Midoriko...
She knew what would happen
to my wish if I lost.
She tried to warn me in her
own way and give me an out,
but I just wouldn't
listen to her.
My wish was to have friends,
so when I lost, I was
hurt and isolated.
But hers, it's
nothing like that.
[ELDORA]
Aah, just shut it!
Hey, I'm the one who gives
the orders, remember?
And once I'm the heroine
of the WIXOSS world,
your time of
punishment's coming!
[ELDORA]
That'll be the day!
[YUZUKI]
Good grief.
If Fumio didn't get through
to her, then I say do it.
[HITOE] If Chiyori wins,
that's another story, but,
if I beat her today,
then I can prevent her
wish from coming true.
But that's what bothers me.
What'll happen to
her if she loses
and her wish gets corrupted?
I wouldn't worry much about it.
Her wish is based on
her love of WIXOSS.
So the reverse of that should
make her end up hating the game.
If you ask me,
that shouldn't make her
current situation any worse.
[CHIYORI growls]
Now I'm really mad!
I'm gonna win, you'll see!
Then I'll never have to lay eyes
on you ever again, you jerk!
[ELDORA]
Talk to the hand.
--[HITOE] Chiyori.
--[CHIYORI] Hm?
I'll do it.
I'll battle you if that's
what you really want to do.
--[ELDORA] Oh?
--[CHIYORI] Uhh... Hm?
Yeah, of course I do!
Yay! It's battle time!
It's history in the making!
Behold, the first chapter
in a new tale of WIXOSS!
A new heroine takes the mantle
and forges into battle!
Are you ready?
Duh, I was born ready!
[HITOE, CHIYORI]
Open!
[TAMA]
A battlefield. One just opened.
It seems that there are others.
More Selectors who hunger
for battle, just like I do.
[TAMA]
I know... But why?
Doesn't it hurt you?
[URITH (I)]
Of course, it does.
A little at least.
But soon enough the
pain will go away.
And I'm going to triumph.
I've stacked sufficient wins,
so just one more will
make my wish come true.
I'll become an LRIG again.
As for you...
You'll come outside and
gain Iona Urazoe's body.
[TAMA gasps]
[TAMA]
But why would I want that?
You told me how
much you like Ruko
and how you want to
be friends with her.
That is your
fondest wish, right?
If that's truly the case,
then you and I have
a mutual interest.
See, if we win this battle,
then this body will be yours.
That'll let you be friends
with Ru, not as a LRIG,
but as a human being like her.
[CHIYORI]
Here we go!
Chiyori Moonlight
Chorizo Attack!
That's the dumbest name yet!
Not bad, Chorizo!
[HITOE]
Are you okay, Yuzuki?
[YUZUKI]
I'm fine!
Hey, look, don't worry
about me, okay?
We can't lose this one!
Yuzuki, now, Grow!
[RUKO] Eldora and
Yuzuki are both strong.
They are, but this match
is already decided.
Right.
Since Yuzuki is
part of a red deck,
she can burn Chiyori's
Ener every turn.
Meaning the odds are stacked
pretty heavily against Chiyori,
aren't they?
They are, and Chiyori
probably doesn't know that.
However...
There's no way that Eldora,
being a LRIG, isn't aware of it.
[gasps]
[RUKO]
Wait a minute!
[YUZUKI yelling]
What? No!
If I keep this up, I'm
gonna lose! Oh, crap!
[ELDORA]
Chiyori, what now?
[CHIYORI]
I-I don't know!
[ELDORA]
Losing's not such a bad thing.
[CHIYORI]
What?
[ELDORA] You'll be able
to retire from battles,
and go back to being
a normal girl again.
Huh?
Eldora, she's--
[RUKO]
I knew it!
Eldora's doing the
same thing as Hitoe!
They're both trying to save
Chiyori from more battles,
from more pain and suffering.
[CHIYORI]
C'mon!
What're you saying?!
--[ELDORA] Hey, girls!
--[YUZUKI, HITOE gasp]
[ELDORA]
I know it's out of place
to ask this during
a battle, but...
Even if I lose here today,
do you think maybe
you guys can be friends
with this weirdo?
What?!
I know she looks all loony now,
but believe it or not,
back when I first met her,
she dressed super-modest,
and to be honest,
--was kind of a nerd.
--[CHIYORI] Hey!
Don't tell 'em that stuff!
[CHIYORI]
Wait. Did you just talk?
[ELDORA]
Yep, and my name is Eldora.
I'm pleased to
meet you, Selector!
Huh?
You're so cute!
Like super-adorable!
[STUDENTS]
Ssh!
[CHIYORI] This is so "you"!
Think it'll look good on me?
You trying to copy my style?
I'm fine with being pals,
but wearing matching
clothes is kinda dorky.
Well, if you don't like it,
then I guess you'll just have
to wear something else then.
[ELDORA]
I'm on paper, I can't!
Oh, yeah! Well, I think
maybe I can fix that!
Just a sec!
[ELDORA]
What?!
--Time to draw!
--[ELDORA] No! Stop!
[ELDORA] She can be a
real handful at times,
but to be honest, I was really
glad she was my Selector.
I'll admit she can be
a bit of a dingbat.
But still, she's a good
person and a lot of fun!
Eldora...
From the very beginning,
you were planning to lose
this battle, weren't you?
[CHIYORI]
Wait, is that true?
[ELDORA]
Not necessarily.
I just thought the odds were
against us, that's all.
It's not like an LRIG can
sway the results or anything.
You meanie! Thanks for
not bothering to tell me!
Big jerk! You suck!
That was so evil of you!
--Take this!
--[ELDORA] Yep, I have to agree.
I'm a jerk, and that's why
we shouldn't be together.
[gasps]
[ELDORA]
I meant it when I said
I was glad you were
my Selector, but still.
You're slow-headed, naive,
and a total spaz.
You dress crazy and
you've gotta be the
goofiest gal I've ever met.
Eldora?
That's you, all right.
And I want you stay just like
that and never change, okay?
[gasps]
Wait, please!
[ELDORA]
All right then, Yuzuki.
Let's get this mess over with.
So Chiyori, what's next? Orochi?
We could go into the Ener Zone!
Or how 'bout going all out
with Arts for our next move?
Stop it!
[gasps]
Chiyori?
[CHIYORI]
Please.
This isn't over yet! Just
come on, stupid brain, work!
Think of a way to turn
the tables in this game!
'Cause if I don't,
it's gonna happen!
I'll be separated
from Eldora forever!
[CHIYORI]
Wait.
Now I've got it!
[ELDORA]
Huh?
[CHIYORI] Eldora, we'll use Life
Cloth with Spell, plus Rush!
[HITOE sighs]
[CHIYORI]
And we'll pair Arts,
Cloth Crush Flash with it
to cause direct damage!
Wait, what?
Chiyori, that's not--
Do it!
[ELDORA]
...going to work.
[CHIYORI gasps]
[ELDORA] With Yuzuki's
deck being what it is,
the odds are against you.
To be honest, if you don't pull
a Shiira within three turns,
Hitoe's gonna win.
[CHIYORI gasps]
I could lose.
[ELDORA]
Uh-uh, no way!
Don't you dare make yourself
lose on purpose, 'kay, Hitoe?
See, I wanna become a human
again one day, you know?
I do.
But if I'm stuck with
an unskilled Selector
like Chiyori here, then
that's never gonna happen.
Eldora...
[ELDORA]
Quit crying and keep going.
If you put a Burst into play,
you still have a
chance of winning.
[CHIYORI gasps]
[ELDORA]
Turn end.
Orochi! Echidna!
Attack!
[ELDORA groans]
Are you okay?
[ELDORA]
It's your turn.
Eldora! You listen!
I promise that I'm
never gonna forget you!
That's turn end.
I swear to you that this isn't
gonna be the final chapter!
And when I get finally
get inside WIXOSS,
I'm gonna be the heroine
of the story, you'll see!
And then I'll make sure you're
the most minor character!
[HITOE]
Orochi.
Now, attack.
[ELDORA yells]
Eldora!
[ELDORA]
Chiyori...
Come on.
We've still got one last turn.
[CHIYORI]
No. Please!
That's enough!
[CHIYORI sobs]
[ELDORA]
But Chiyori...
Despite the trash
talk, I did like you.
[gasps]
[ELDORA]
Turn end.
I guess that's it.
All that's left...
is the finishing blow.
[CHIYORI sobs]
[foosteps]
You're a bit late.
"Aki-'ovely."
[AKIRA]
Not today.
No Aki-lucky.
No Aki-lovely.
I'm the one who'll beat you,
the one who'll save you.
[AKIRA]
Just... Akira Aoi.
--[VOICES chattering]
--[MAYU] Shut up.
[MAYU]
Shut up.
Shut up!
But that's wrong!
You're lying!
That's not how it works!
Or else, it's completely wrong.
Absolutely wrong!
[RUKO] Next time:
"This Warmth is at its Limit."