Wha--
It's Tama?
What's happening?
It's really Tama.
[YUZUKI]
But why?
So that's how it is, huh?
She's here.
And she's safe.
I was afraid I'd lost her.
Hey, Tama!
But why... did she
change Selectors?
[YUZUKI]
That's only half of the problem.
I'm wondering why Urith
is even battling.
She's supposed to be
carrying out your wish
right now, isn't she?
Well, she's not
breaking any rules.
Besides, to a certain extent, my
wish has already been granted.
But what does she have
to gain from fighting?
[YUZUKI]
Spill it.
There's something
you're not telling us.
About Urith and about Tama.
You're wrong.
I wish I knew.
But I don't.
That's just like her.
Tasteless and cruel.
[MAYU]
Poor little Tama.
It's a frightening
world out there.
You're only going
to be hurt again.
Lucky us, we get to go first.
Now Grow.
[CHIYORI giggles]
Oh yeah!
Hoo-yeah!
[ELDORA] Try not to
humiliate us too badly.
Tama! Don't do it!
I'm going to have to ask you
to stop distracting my LRIG.
The only one she
needs to talk to is me.
Wish Crisis!
[TAMA gasps]
[ELDORA grunts]
So strong! Awesome!
You're gonna blow me up!
I mean, unless
I blow you up first!
Oh, dude!
We're like rivals, huh?
[ELDORA growls] Glad
somebody's enjoying themselves.
[CHIYORI]
Chorizo the Fantasy! Attack!
That is not the name of my move!
Okay. Then attack with
Cloth Crash Flash!
[ELDORA grunts]
[whoops] She's strong!
I'm so done...
[ELDORA screams]
It's getting hard to watch.
[YUZUKI] I think Chiyori's
as good as done for.
This is wrong.
No, Tama! Stop it!
Ru...
Huh. It's all right--
you don't have
to listen to her anymore.
She threw you away, remember?
[TAMA gasps]
She did not!
We just--
Use Spell: Get Bound.
[TAMA grunts] No.
Oh boy, that's bad.
--[TAMA growls]
--[ELDORA yells]
[RUKO gasps]
It seems Tama's getting along
fine without her old friend.
[RUKO]
Huh?
[TAMA snarls]
[ELDORA groans]
[ELDORA]
Yaaugh!
If she can have fun in
battle, why can't you?
[RUKO gasps]
[IONA] She has a new partner,
but nothing else has changed.
Tama...
[IONA]
I fought for this, Ru.
I fought for you.
We were meant to be
together, to win together.
[bells ringing]
[gasps]
[TAMA whimpers]
That's not true.
And Tama's...
not having fun at all.
[IONA]
Ah...?
Eldora, Grow!
Attack with Kozame!
[ELDORA yells]
[TAMA]
Ru...
I'm sorry...
[RUKO]
Tama...
[TAMA]
I was a bad girl.
That's why I got taken
away from you, right?
ARTS: Baroque Defense.
[CHIYORI]
Rrgh! Sh-Shira!
Attack!
Or not...
[CHIYORI]
Aw, c'mon, do it!
She's using a card
that blocks offense!
Would you pay attention?!
Heh.
[ELDORA screams]
[TAMA]
This is awful...
I thought Battles were
supposed to be fun.
I thought I liked getting strong
and winning, but I hate this.
If I don't have Ru,
then there's no point.
[URITH (I)]
Salvage!
I don't wanna!
[IONA]
I think you were right.
She's really not having fun.
Stop it...
[TAMA whimpers]
[RUKO]
This is all my fault...
I'm sorry, Tama!
Huh...?
I was sure beating
Iona would be the end.
I'd given up any hope
of coming back.
I thought I was gonna turn
into an LRIG for sure.
But that didn't matter to me.
If I could change Yuzuki back,
if I could give you
a better life,
it was a small price to pay.
At least, that's what
I tried to convince myself.
It's okay.
I missed you so much!
Everything feels empty
without you to share it with me!
[TAMA]
I did bad.
I was too scared.
[RUKO]
So was I.
If I had just told you
how I felt,
then this wouldn't
have happened!
I was the one who
needed to trust you!
[TAMA whimpers]
[RUKO] I was acting like
some kind of lonely hero
and I got stuck
thinking that I needed
to push everyone else away.
But I should've let you help me.
'Cause you're my best friend
in the whole world, Tama!
[RUKO whimpers]
[YUZUKI]
It's not over.
[IONA]
Her best friend.
--[ELDORA sighs]
--[CHIYORI sobs]
Huh?
Jeez. I understand why
they're crying, but you too?
[CHIYORI]
I love it!
Their friendship
is so beautiful!
And now they gotta
fight each other,
which is one of
the best plot twists ever!
It's so cliché! It's like
a TV show come true!
Nothing beats a good cliché!
I'm telling you, they're like
the bread and butter of my soul!
Well, I'm so glad you're
enjoying this little drama
while I'm getting
destroyed out there!
[CHIYORI]
Wha...? Huh?
[ELDORA] Pretty sure they're
gonna finish me off
with the next move. And then...
Ru...
Tama...
You naughty thing.
Thinking of another girl
while you're doing it with me?
You should be ashamed.
I guess I'm not enough.
Let's finish this.
Arc Aura!
[ELDORA screams]
[BOTH whimper]
[CHIYORI sighs]
Tama?
[TAMA whimpers]
Listen.
[YUZUKI]
Hey, hold on!
Urith!
Give her back!
[URITH (I)]
If you want her that bad,
why don't you battle me for her?
[RUKO gasps]
[TAMA]
No!
Ru, you don't have to battle!
She can't make you!
[URITH (I)]
Hmph. No rush though,
you come find me when
you're good and ready.
Work on her for me, Iona.
Till next time,
Miss Pain-in-the-Ass.
Tama!
[TAMA whimpers]
Ru...
[HITOE]
Don't worry. We can fix this.
[RUKO]
Yeah. Thanks.
At least I know Tama's okay.
Not only that, it seems like
she feels the same way I do.
Anyway, thanks for
sticking with me
through all this mess, you guys.
[CHIYORI]
Nice job on that plot twist!
A tragedy among friends
and a rival for me! Ooh!
You gotta admit,
that was pretty sweet!
Hello, Chiyori.
[YUZUKI]
You're still here?
You guys should be way
more pumped about this!
Seriously, Eldora,
what the hell?!
[HITOE] Why would you
do that after we told you
how dangerous Battles were?
Do you even care what
happens to Chiyori?
Gimme a break!
Both of us spent a long time
working all this out.
She can be pretty
stubborn, though.
[CHIYORI]
Let's see.
Here it is!
Wa-pa-pow!
[BOTH]
Huh?
What is that?
[CHIYORI]
Chorizo De Ibéricoña The Second!
Oh, I think I've
eaten chorizo before,
but what does sausage
have to do with this?
Nothing--it's the name I'm gonna
have when I turn into an LRIG!
[HITOE, RUKO]
Huh?
There you have it.
There is no talking
sense into this girl.
But wait...
You lost your first match to me,
and now your second to Urith?
You're already down
to your last one?
[YUZUKI]
You gotta stop!
No way!
Sure, I lost a couple,
but I won three already!
That means my wish could
come true at any time!
Yeah, but if you
lose one more time,
that wish is gonna be corrupted!
The main character in
the novel lost twice too,
but she didn't give up.
She beat her rival
and got her wish!
She passes out, then finds
herself in the White Garden
when she wakes up!
White Garden?
What is that?
Duh, it's the
hyper-dimensional white void?!
White void? Seriously?
That sounds suspiciously
like the white room I went to
when I became an LRIG.
No way!
You mean they talk
about that in the book?!
What?
I so gave you a copy
of it, you should know!
You're telling me
you didn't read it?
I've... been
kind of busy lately.
This is really getting weird.
Hey, Chiyori?
Can we see that book?
The answers we need might be
right in front of us.
[RUKO]
"WIXOSS.
The Wings of Lament Mark the
Dreams of the Ruined Land."
By Fumio Futase.
[RUKO]
"In a future not far from now,
mysterious creatures
known as LRIGs
appear all throughout
the world."
[RUKO] "Strange and beautiful,
these fairy-like entities
form pacts with young girls,
promising that they can
make their wishes come true.
However, for that to happen,
the girls must first
battle other LRIGs,
and collect something known
as WIXOSS factors
within their body.
A certain young girl forms a
partnership with a certain LRIG
and is drawn into
the battle to make
her wish come true.
When she tastes
victory at last,
her wish is not granted, but
instead,
she suddenly finds herself
lost in the labyrinth of time:
White Garden."
[HITOE] It's just like
Yuzuki was saying.
That must be the white room
with the window, right?
[RUKO] They don't use the word
"Selector,"
but everything else here
matches up almost perfectly.
[YUZUKI] Yeah, they barely
even spiced it up.
Ugh! And look, now the
Dark Lady of Atonement
shows up--her name is Cocoon!
Yoink!
She's the ruler
of White Garden.
An almighty being that
holds dominion over
all WIXOSS Battles!
[YUZUKI] Is she like
the last boss or something?
[CHIYORI groans]
I can't believe it ends
on such a cliffhanger!
[groans] Dang it! The suspense!
It's killing me!
Yeah, that's, uh...
[HITOE]
"Cocoon"?
Ah?
The word "mayu" means
"cocoon" doesn't it?
[gasps]
[YUZUKI]
That's her!
Whoever wrote this must know!
All right, then.
We've got ourselves a lead!
The next step is to find her.
[HITOE]
Fumio Futase.
She got her start by posting
stories on the internet.
I guess it was like
fan fiction at first,
but some editor liked the story,
and it became official canon.
[YUZUKI] Any information on when
the third book is coming out?
They say it's on hold.
You think she's
a Selector like us?
Maybe.
But then it seems strange
that she would glamorize this.
[YUZUKI]
Mm-hmm.
Especially if she's heard about
Mayu and that White Room.
That means she also knows
how dangerous it is
to keep having Battles.
We need to find
some way to meet her.
Huh?
I want every bit of
information she's got.
[YUZUKI]
Okay, but like, what?
She might know more about Mayu.
Or more about Tama.
There was something
you said before,
about Tama maybe being one
of the "special" ones.
[IONA]
Mm?
[gasps]
[MAYU] That is to say,
some Eternal Girls are more
"special" than others.
[MAYU] You may lack the power
to create this fairy tale ending
you so desire, but there is
magic yet in this world.
[TAMA]
Somewhere deep down.
I feel like I might know how.
Like I can help all the LRIGs.
Maybe turn them back to normal.
There's something
we still don't know.
Something that might
help save her.
And everyone else, I hope.
Wait a second,
where did Chiyori go?
[CHIYORI]
Yargh!
[HITOE, RUKO gasp]
[HATSU]
Too bad.
That's six wins
in a row for Grandma.
[CHIYORI groans]
You are too good!
If you can't
even win one,
I'll have to eat this entire
box of snacks myself.
[CHIYORI gasps] Could you be
the Sorceress of Blood?!
The Queen of the Innocent
and Danger Zone
of all WIXOSS players
in the world?!
[HATSU chuckles]
My goodness, perhaps I am!
How 'bout a new bet:
if you beat me, I'll tell you.
Hi, girls!
Would you like to join
us for a few rounds?
Uh...
Maybe later.
[HITOE giggles]
[HITOE]
Ooh! Yes!
We found it!
It's the author's website!
And she updated recently.
[HITOE]
To: Fumio Futase.
Subject: Selectors.
Excuse us for the sudden
E-mail. We read your book.
We'll be very up front.
We're Selectors.
Are you aware of Selectors?
If so, then, uhm...
Please allow us... the
opportunity to speak with you.
Ruko Kominato.
Hitoe Uemura.
Does that all sound good to you?
[RUKO]
Mm-hmm.
[CHIYORI]
Catch you later!
We'll give you a call
when we hear back from her!
You gotta come with us, okay?
[CHIYORI]
You bet I will!
[BOTH laugh]
You think... she'll respond?
Well... I hope so, since
we've got so many questions.
We still don't know what
really happened with Akira.
Or with Urith.
[RUKO]
Mm...
Either way, I don't think
it's a coincidence
that she ended up
with Tama as her LRIG.
Huh?
Yeah, like me and Yuzuki.
It is kinda fishy.
So yeah.
Mayu's plotting something.
Then we have to stop her.
Well, obviously.
But I'm just trying to figure
out why she's doing it.
Yeah, no kidding!
Does she like watching us
suffer, or what?!
[IONA] You're looking
at this all wrong.
Stop trying to apply
rules or logic to it.
Those are just a veil to
entangle players even further.
Mayu's plan isn't very complex.
All the players are her toys.
And now she's having
her way with us.
So yes, she likes watching
you suffer tremendously.
It's that simple?
She's made it clear
how petty she can be.
She'll just keep pushing back.
Find new ways to torment you.
Then that settles it.
We're gonna make her pay!
[HITOE]
We'll see you later.
[RUKO
'Kay.
[YUZUKI]
Oh. One last thing.
[RUKO]
Ah?
I know today wasn't
exactly great,
but on the upside, you saw Tama.
You two are the perfect team.
I'm sure you'll be
together again someday.
[HITOE] Mm-hmm! I feel like
we're making progress already,
so it's only a matter of time.
Just hang in there.
Oh, Hitoe. Yuzuki.
Thank you for that.
[YUZUKI]
See ya!
[HITOE]
Good night.
[RUKO]
[IONA]
Disgusting.
[gasps]
Are you kidding me?
What a joke.
They make me sick.
Huh...?
[AKIRA'S MOM]
Akira, Iona's here!
[AKIRA whimpers]
[URITH (I)]
How has she been?
Better, I hope.
[AKIRA'S MOM]
Oh, yes, all thanks to you.
You're welcome here any time.
I'm so glad she has
such a good friend.
[URITH (I)]
It's nothing.
[AKIRA'S MOM]
Akira? Did you hear me?
Ugh, I'm sorry. Go on in.
[URITH (I)]
Thank you.
[gasps]
I'm afraid I'm going to have
to ask for another favor.
[gasps] Anything...
Anything for you...
[AKIRA sighs]
[URITH (I)]
Akira...
So precious...
[TAMA whimpers]
[IONA]
I can't stomach that girl.
And her stupid smile.
[RUKO]
Huh...?
[CHIYORI groans]
You really think
Fumio Futase lives here?
Yeah, unless she was
lying to us in the e-mail.
I-I can't take this!
I'm so nervous, my heart's
gonna shoot into orbit!
[ELDORA] Sorry, I know
it's hard to believe,
but she can be pretty
shy sometimes!
[CHIYORI] Oh my gosh, oh my
gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh,
oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my
gosh, oh my gooooshhh...
[CHIYORI whines, squeals]
[doorbell]
Hi, um. This is Ruko--you
sent me an e-mail?
[ALL gasp]
[RUKO]
Uh, hello?
Um, may we come in, please?
[BOTH gasp]
[RUKO]
Anyone here?
[YUZUKI]
So what now?
[FUMIO]
White room.
Mayu.
Large window.
White room.
Mayu.
Large window.
White room.
Mayu.
Hello?
Sorry we kind of just
let ourselves in.
Are you...?
[FUMIO]
Yes.
[ALL gasp]
I'm Fumio.
Fumio Futase.
[RUKO] You know something about
WIXOSS that we don't,
and I'd like to
hear what that is.
[FUMIO]
Battle me for your wish.
If you win, I'll tell you
everything you wanna know.
[URITH (I)] How much do you
think this author really knows?
[FUMIO] I've never seen
anything like this before.
[RUKO] Next time: "This
Impatience Isn't Awakening."