[YUZUKI]
That was the first time.
[HANAYO] What?
[YUZUKI] I've never
told anyone how I felt.
You were the first person
I've ever been
completely honest with.
[HANAYO] Yuzuki...
[YUZUKI]
Thank you for that, Hanayo.
Ru, dear,
that's sweet of you, but you're
going to be late for school.
Huh? What time is it?
You get going,
I'll take care of the rest.
Uhh, thanks!
[HATSU chuckles]
[RUKO gasps]
Huh...?
[TAMA yawns]
[TAMA] Oh, good morning, Ru.
Hey, Tama. School time!
Can't I sleep just
another five minutes?
I guess, but you're
coming with either way!
[KAZUKI gasps]
U-Um, Yuzuki... I'm sorry!
[KAZUKI] I'm takin' off!
[LANDLADY]
All alone today, huh?
Where's your sister?
Shouldn't you two be together?
Huh?! The heck's
that supposed to mean?
[LANDLADY] Ah, kids...
[GIRL 9A] Akira's still missing?
Wow.
[GIRL 9B] Yeah, they
interviewed a girl
from her school in that article.
It's like she just disappeared.
Nobody's seen her
for almost a week.
[TAMA]
You're gonna miss the train. Ru!
[ANNOUNCER]
Now departing.
Yuzuki...
[RUKO] We were getting
along so well, but now...
[YUZUKI] God, I hate this--
We can't be friends anymore.
[RUKO] No, we can't.
She's right. 'Cause...
...I refuse to have
any more battles.
But Yuzuki won't stop battling
until her wish comes true.
No matter how many people
she hurts in the process.
[RUKO] But I... I
can't live like that.
[students murmuring]
[BOY 9A] You serious?
[BOY 9B] Pretty freaky, huh?
[GIRL 9C] The twins?
[GIRL 9D] Yeah, can you
believe they're a couple?
[BOY 9C]
Like... incest for real?
[GIRL 9E] No way!
[BOY 9D]
Wow, so the rumors are true?
[BOY 9E] Oh, you think
they've already done it?
[BOY 9D] Duh, what do you think?
[BOY 9E] Aw, barf!
[GIRL 6B]
Don't blame yourself, Honoka.
[GIRL 6A] There's no way
you could have known
he was like that.
[GIRL 6B] And I used
to think he was cool.
[GIRL 6A] He's just gross!
[gasping]
I assume you're the one
responsible for all this?
[GIRL 6B]
It's not her fault, jackass!
Yeah, people wouldn't talk
if you and your
sister acted normal.
No, jerk,
I didn't do a thing.
I just told a few friends
what you said to me.
You know, how upset you got
when you heard the rumor.
[GIRL 6B] Honoka was worried
about you, you jerk!
I really wasn't trying
to start anything...
Although, your sister does
act kind of weird sometimes.
You know, forget you. I'm done.
Nobody talks bad
about my sister!
[HONOKA gasps]
Don't act like I'm some
kinda villain! So rude!
[GIRL 6B] Geez, you're horrible!
[GIRL 6A] Guh, no wonder
people are saying
he and his
sister are an item!
[GIRL 9F] Apologize to her!
[GIRL 9G] What a weirdo!
[GIRL 9H]
You make my skin crawl!
[BOY 9F] Yeah, with her brother!
[BOY 9G] Aw, nasty!
[BOY 9H] Too bad.
I thought she was hot.
[HANAYO (Y)] There you are.
[KAZUKI] Yuzuki.
So I heard you've
been telling people
not to talk about me.
Is that for real?
[KAZUKI] Yeah...
[HANAYO (Y)]
That's sweet of you,
but it's not
really necessary.
It's not gossip if it's true.
[KAZUKI] Wait a minute,
what do you mean by that?
I mean...
I'm in love with you.
Wha--?
I've been in love with you
ever since we were kids.
But I never told you before.
I didn't want to scare you
off, but I've felt this way...
...my entire life.
Always.
[FRIEND A] You've got a crush on
that cute boy Goto, don't you?
[FRIEND B]
Heh! Uh-huh!
[FRIEND C]
And you, Yuzuki?
[YUZUKI giggles]
[HANAYO (Y)] While my friends
were always chatting about
what boy they had
a crush on that week...
[FRIEND 9C]
C'mon, spill it!
[YUZUKI]
Huh?
[FRIEND 9A] Everyone said who
they liked! Now it's your turn.
[FRIEND 9B]
Who's your secret crush?
Uh... Sorry, but I don't have
one. At least not right now.
[FRIEND 9C]
Liar-liar, pants on fire!
[YUZUKI] I'm just not really
into any of the guys
in our class.
[FRIEND 9B]
You're so lying!
[YUZUKI] No, I'm not!
[FRIEND 9A]
Tell the truth!
[YUZUKI] I am, doofus!
[HANAYO (Y)] I couldn't tell
anyone how I really felt.
[FRIEND 9D]
So, um... your brother.
Do you know...
...if there's a girl he likes?
[YUZUKI] Um, well,
to tell the truth,
he's always talking about
how girls are gross.
Even when he's watching TV.
If like, a kissing
scene comes on,
he always changes the channel.
[HANAYO (Y)]
I lied to all my friends, and...
...I lied to you.
The one I love.
For the longest time,
I thought maybe it was
best to keep it like that.
[HANAYO] Are you sure?
Can you really live like this?
[YUZUKI] Yeah.
But no matter what, I will
still love Kazuki forever.
And it doesn't matter
if he finds a girlfriend,
or gets married,
or even if he has kids.
I'll just keep living this
lie for the rest of my life,
'til I'm old and alone.
If this is the only way I can
love him, so be it, I guess.
But then...
One day...
[YUZUKI] A card game?
[KAZUKI] Yeah, it's pretty fun.
[YUZUKI screams]
Huh? Hey, what's the matter?
Huh?
[HANAYO]
You must be my Selector!
Huh?
[HANAYO] My name's
Hanayo. Nice to meet you!
Whoa, that card
just talked to me!
Wait, the card did what now?
It talked. You mean,
you didn't hear?
I'm not craz--!
He can't hear me.
As a matter of fact,
the only ones who can
are Selectors like you.
Okay, but what have
I been selected for?
[YUZUKI] My wish...
can come true?
[HANAYO] Mm-hmm.
Whether you believe that or not,
though, is entirely up to you.
[HANAYO]
You do have a wish, right?
I'm stuck inside a card.
Your secret is safe with me.
I... love...
[HANAYO] What?
...Kazuki, I... love him.
O-kay. So, who?
Oh, wait, you mean your brother?
[YUZUKI] Yes, I love
him. I love Kazuki.
I love Kazuki!
I love my brother, okay?!
[YUZUKI sobs]
[YUZUKI] I love him...
I know. I know it's not right.
And... I know it's not normal!
But I still want
to be with him!
I want to spend the
rest of my life with him!
I want more than that.
I want to be
Kazuki's girlfriend!
[HANAYO] All right.
Let's make it happen.
And we'll do it... together.
So, then...
Your wish was for...?
[HANAYO (Y)] You once called
my strategy straightforward.
That's how I have
to be in life, too.
I have to be
straightforward with you.
The same way I was with Hanayo.
[YUZUKI]
That was the first time.
[HANAYO] What?
[YUZUKI] I've never
told anyone how I felt.
You were the
very first person...
...I've ever been
completely honest with.
[HANAYO] Yuzuki...
Thank you for that, Hanayo...
I didn't care what it
would take to accomplish.
If there was any chance
of being with you,
even if it meant me
getting hurt or dying...
I'd take it because I love you.
Do you feel the same about me?
[KAZUKI grunts]
[BOY 9I] Kazuki? No, he
hasn't come back from lunch yet.
Oh, thanks.
[GIRL 6A] O-M-G! Would
you look who's here!
Ew, it's the "brother-lover!"
[GIRL 9G] That
is so skeevy!
[GIRLS giggle maliciously]
[trains clattering]
[RUKO] A wish.
[RUKO] One that
you want so badly
that you're willing to hurt
yourself... or someone else.
[YUZUKI] Next time we meet,
I'll be a new me!
No more regrets!
I'll finally be Kazuki's
girlfriend for real!
[RUKO] I tried to
stop her, but I couldn't.
She didn't care what happened.
[RUKO] I guess, since I don't
have a wish, I can't understand.
[IONA] But it is
the nature of battle.
And our nature as well.
Both mine...
...and yours.
I'm not... like her.
[TAMA] Ru?
[RUKO gasps]
You're feeling sad, huh?
[RUKO] What?
You know. 'Cause you
and Yuzuki and Hitoe
were all friends,
but now you're not?
Tama will still be
your friend, though!
Let's battle!
Well, even if we don't get
to battle, we're friends.
Forever!
Tama.
I'm sorry I like to battle
so much, but... you did.
So, I'll just stop!
Thank you, Tama. You rock.
Yep!
[TAMA giggles]
[HITOE] Excuse me.
[RUKO] Hitoe?
What the--? Why are you here?
Wait a minute, does this
mean you're all better now
and you remember me?
[TAMA] Ru!
Look, Hitoe has an LRIG!
But how?
[HITOE] You...
You're a Selector, aren't you?
Please let me challenge
you to a battle.
Wha--?
No. How are you
a Selector again?!
Battle me. Please.
Just say yes.
I can't.
No, I won't.
Look, I'm real sorry.
But I've decided not
to battle people ever again.
[YUZUKI] Oh, yeah?
Then why are you still
keeping Tama around?
Yuzuki?
[YUZUKI]
Guess I can't blame you.
You two are
practically best friends.
[RUKO] Where are you?
[YUZUKI] Speaking of friends,
can't you do a favor for
two of your former ones?
Just for old times' sake?
Come on! Where are you? Yuzuki?
[RUKO gasps]
Hmph.
Yuzuki, no!
Hey, hey, long time no see!
No, not really.
You're an LRIG?
This can't be real.
It's nuts.
I mean...
That can't be you.
It's me all right.
Here, let me prove it.
[RUKO gasps]
That scrunchie, it's--!
Yeah, the one I bought
with you two that day.
Guess the three of us
can't stay apart, huh?
Yuzuki, what... happened?
[YUZUKI] S'pose I owe
you an explanation,
and I'll be happy
to give you one.
If you agree... to
a battle with Hitoe.
And risk hurting her?
There's no freaking way!
You'd be doing
it to help her.
So her wish
can be granted.
And so mine can, too.
[HITOE] I need to fight.
[YUZUKI] Ruko... Please.
[RUKO]
If it's for my friends, I--
Fine, I'll do it.
[YUZUKI] Thank you.
[HITOE &amp; RUKO] Open!
Damn it all. I hate this!
'Kay! Grow, Tama!
On it!
All right, Yuzuki! Now
you tell me what happened!
Well, for starters,
I won my final battle.
And then...
At long last
my wish came true.
Since you've made
your decision,
let us join together
for one final attack.
Now, the oath.
Do you remember it?
Yeah.
It's, uh...
"I accept..."
"...the laws of the Selector."
"I accept the laws
of the Selector".
And, um...
[BOTH]
"And upon this sacred oath,
a new Eternal Girl
shall be born!"
[BOTH] Adamasphere!
What?
Then does that mean
you're not the only Yuzuki?
[YUZUKI] Not anymore.
[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO] So Hanayo...
...became you?
Obviously that wasn't
what I was expecting.
But after we finished the oath,
I found out what it really means
to become an "Eternal Girl."
My wish?
Now it gets granted to her.
[door opens]
I made this
drawing in pre-school.
The princess is
supposed to be me.
And this black scribble,
you wanna guess?
Uh...
It's supposed to be
of you as my prince.
This drawing is of us
on our wedding day.
But the other kids told
me it was dirty and wrong.
So I did this.
Scribbled over it,
tried to cover it up.
Again and again.
But...
It was still there.
Yeah, I get it.
Try as I might, these
feelings won't go away, either.
Yuzuki.
I love you.
And in the same way you love me.
I mean it!
I've felt this
way a long time,
but because we're family,
I kept those feelings
to myself just like you.
I did my best
to block them out.
But to hell with that,
I can't do it anymore!
I love you.
Listen:
I don't care what people think.
Or what they say.
If it means I have to give up
anything and everything
to be with you, so be it!
I love you, Yuzuki!
I love you!
I swear it.
[HANAYO (Y)]
I love you, too, Kazuki.
So very much.
[HANAYO (Y)] I'm so happy...
The wish has
finally come true.
[RUKO] So not just your life...
she took your wish
all for herself?
[VOICE]
And now...
You become an LRIG.
[HITOE screams]
[HITOE sobs softly]
[YUZUKI] Once the
Selector is replaced,
they become
another person's LRIG.
[HITOE gasps]
Nice to meet you...
...Selector.
[YUZUKI]
So whether we win or lose,
it's the Selectors who suffer,
and the LRIGs who benefit.
Maybe they were fighting
to become human again
all along.
And yet, she did
grant my wish.
Holding up her end of this
perverse contract, I suppose.
And I became an Eternal Girl...
To repeat the cycle.
Get it now?
That's the ugly truth
behind this game!
[YUZUKI] Hanayo.
[TAMA] Stop it!
[YUZUKI] Thank you, Hanayo.
[TAMA]
My memory is still too fuzzy.
[YUZUKI] How could you do this?
We were friends!
[TAMA] I don't know, okay?
[YUZUKI]
She still kept her word.
[RUKO] Next time:
"That Stranded Emotion."