[MAYU]
Another wish.
Falling like
a star from the sky.
[MAYU]
Wait.
How strange.
It seems that one
had escaped my notice.
[IONA] Even if I wanted to,
I could never grant Ruko's wish.
Releasing all of
the LRIGs from their cards
simply isn't possible.
And if I can't grant the wish,
that means Tama couldn't either.
But Ru still believes.
She still persists.
[RUKO]
Hello?
Sorry we kind of
just let ourselves in.
Are you...?
[ALL gasp]
[RUKO] So, you're the one
who wrote the novel?
[FUMIO]
As I said.
I'm Fumio Futase.
That's crazy. I didn't
realize you were so young.
You're in high school?
And you're published?
[YUZUKI] Yeah, that's a
Fujikou High uniform.
I wonder if anybody knows.
[FUMIO]
Hmph.
Cutting to the chase, which one
of you wants to battle first?
Then you are one!
A Selector!
I would be delighted to meet any
of you on the stage of battle.
[gasps]
A high school author Selector,
rockin' a bad girl haircut?!
Now that is the most
awesome character ever!
I'm transforming into
Burning Chorizo mode!
I think there's been a
misunderstanding.
We didn't come here
to battle you.
[FUMIO]
Is that so?
Excuse me for
being presumptuous,
but what other reason could
Selectors have to meet up?
[YUZUKI]
Just because we're Selectors
doesn't mean we have to battle.
And now I'm beginning to
think you're mocking me.
You're saying none of you
have a wish worth fighting for?
Even if you win,
they don't come true.
Not how you'd think, at least.
If you'll let us tell you
the truth about this, Fumio,
I think you might
change your mind.
Spreading the
noble truth? I see!
You're an LRIG--Don't
act like you don't know!
Yes. I am frightfully
well-informed.
And I'm not
the only one, either.
Let me be frank:
This "hidden truth"
behind our wishes?
I know exactly what happens.
And it still doesn't
change my opinion.
[RUKO]
What...?
[URITH (I) "She is
the ruler of White Garden.
An almighty being
that holds dominion
over all WIXOSS Battles.
The truth lingers on
her lips, revealing the laws
of this twisted world".
Huh.
Say.
How much do you think
this author really knows?
[TAMA groans]
Heh. Aren't you just
a barrel of laughs?
Ru...
No... that doesn't make sense.
[ANN] Even if she knows
the same facts,
that doesn't mean
she has to come
to the same conclusion as you.
[FUMIO]
Yes, it's all quite cruel.
If a Selector loses three times,
her wish becomes tainted.
But if she manages to
win enough battles,
it only serves to grant
freedom to her LRIG.
Not truly free though,
the LRIG must now grant
her former Selector's wish.
That Selector, meanwhile,
becomes imprisoned as an LRIG.
Anything I missed?
[YUZUKI gasps]
If you know all that,
then why keep battling?!
Yeah! No good can
ever come of this!
[FUMIO]
Interesting.
You're among a chosen few,
yet you deny your very
existence as Selectors.
I'll admit, that's
a new one for me.
Plenty of Selectors have
approached me, by the way.
All of 'em dying to battle.
And after reading my novel,
how could they resist?
[YUZUKI]
What do you expect?
That's because they
read your novel!
Fumio, we don't want to fight.
But I do think you know
something about WIXOSS
that we don't, and I'd
like to hear what that is.
[FUMIO]
Obtaining knowledge.
That's your wish then,
in a sense?
Huh?
[FUMIO] You're a Selector,
so act like one.
Battle me for your wish.
If you win, I'll tell you
everything you wanna know.
[HITOE]
I dunno, Ruko.
Nothing's ever free.
If it is worthwhile, there
is always struggle for it.
However, I shall warn you
that Fumio has never lost once.
How 'bout you?
[RUKO]
I haven't lost, either.
[FUMIO] Then unfortunately,
it'll lack the excitement
of a higher-stakes battle,
but on the upside,
neither of us has much to lose.
[RUKO grunts]
[CHIYORI]
Hey! Yoo-hoo, guys!
If Ruko wusses out, then
let Chorizo give it a go!
--[RUKO] Huh?
--[YUZUKI] What? No!
You gotta be crazy!
Oh, boy... Here we go again.
You realize you're out of the
game after the next loss, right?
Nevermind.
[FUMIO]
That's fine.
I'm not particular
about my opponent.
[gasps]
[CHIYORI]
Me, me!
Well, looks like we have
a battle on our hands.
Unless anyone objects, that is.
--[CHIYORI] Woo-hoo!
--[RUKO] No, let me fight.
[HITOE, CHIYORI]
Huh?
[YUZUKI]
Ruko?!
I kinda called it.
I can't let Chiyori battle
such a strong player
when she's already
had her second loss.
She robbed me!
[ELDORA]
Be grateful!
[FUMIO]
Hmph.
Iona. You ready?
[FUMIO]
Huh?
Is that your LRIG?
I, uh, nevermind, let's go.
[FUMIO, RUKO]
Open!
[ANN giggles]
How lovely.
Finally time for a dance!
[YUZUKI] Damn it, we were
just supposed to talk to her!
I hate this.
[RUKO] I know Tama
told me not to battle.
But it's like I can't get away!
The curtain rises,
now let us enter the stage.
Okay, I go first.
Now Grow!
Summon Code Maze
Triumph and Clay!
Grow.
Banish Triumphal Arch
with Fallen Bind.
[IONA grunts]
Iona, are you--?
Your concern isn't necessary.
Just win.
Okay.
Now I use Slash Miracle
to Banish Puri!
I see.
Then Puri's skill brings
Surrelis to my hand.
[IONA grunting]
I-I didn't think.
Without Tama, she's a mess.
She had better pull it
together and fast!
Ruko...
[FUMIO]
That LRIG isn't normal.
[ANN] As usual,
you're quick to catch on.
Just as I thought.
I can't put my finger on it.
But somehow, she's
different than me.
--[FUMIO] Hmm...
--[ANN] Still...
She doesn't seem to get along
with her Selector at all.
Whatever power they
possess is wasted.
[FUMIO] Then let's see if
we can force it out of them.
[gasps]
[IONA grunts]
[panting]
[RUKO]
I'm-I'm gonna lose.
She's not just strong, she's
always one step ahead of us.
I don't know what
I'm supposed to do.
[IONA] Well, for starters, why
don't you stop cowering in fear?
[gasps] That's not
what I'm doing at all!
[IONA] Before, you had
a hunger for battle.
You had the conviction
to tear down any wall,
to defy any limit.
Um...
That's not true...
You wanna save your friends?
Right now, you don't have
the strength to save anyone.
[gasps]
[IONA]
Not Yuzuki,
and certainly not all the other
girls transformed into LRIGs.
[RUKO]
I'll find a way!
I have to, somehow.
No one should have to
suffer like Hitoe did.
Having such an innocent wish
twisted into something so cruel.
Or Yuzuki, who fought and fought
only to have her whole
life taken from her.
I don't care what it takes!
I'll find a way to end
this game, no matter what!
Now Grow!
Just 'cause you say it,
doesn't make it true.
[gasps]
It infuriates me that
I lost to someone
who spews such
idealistic nonsense.
That I lost to an utter fool,
who'd naïvely help others
before herself.
That I lost to someone
so disgustingly pure.
[IONA sighs]
I didn't mean to--
[IONA]
You have to find yourself again!
I became your LRIG
because I b elieved in you--
Because I knew you were strong!
So find that strength!
The strength you had
when you were with Tama!
Or else, she'll be one more
friend you fail to save!
[gasps]
[RUKO]
Tama...
That's right.
I have a wish
worth fighting for,
and I don't care if
I have to play this game
to make it happen.
I don't care what I have to do.
I'll save my friends!
[FUMIO] I know this sounds
ironic coming from me,
but this isn't a novel.
Let's not get carried away.
Just because you have
a character moment,
doesn't mean that you'll win.
[ANN]
Haa...
[ANN grunts]
[FUMIO]
Hmph.
I can't lose here.
I won't back down ever again!
[RUKO]
Iona, Grow!
--You're kidding.
--[ANN gasps]
No way!
She's at level four already!
That's as high as it goes!
What is she... doing?
[FUMIO]
What the--?
I've never seen anything
like this before.
[IONA]
This is it. Ruko's power.
This is what Tama felt.
What she believed in.
[ANN]
That's not fair!
How did you do that?!
Nobody can even do that!
There is no level 5!
Oh, wow! Yes! It's on now!
A forbidden power that
awakens when the hero
is backed into a corner!
Super exciting and super cliché!
[YUZUKI] Looks like Ruko's
finally having fun again!
[HITOE]
Mm-hmm!
Even though it took a Battle,
I'm still happy for her.
[YUZUKI]
Whatever works, right?
[ANN whimpers]
Any chance...
...I could ask...
to give me an encore...?
Sorry, show's over.
[ANN screams]
[ANN whimpers]
I gave it my best...
I'm sorry...
No. It's fine.
Thank you for what
you said, Iona.
And the whole transforming
thing was pretty awesome, too.
[IONA]
Why?
Why did I tell her that?
[RUKO giggles]
Well, I certainly
wasn't expecting that.
Your LRIG's strange.
[RUKO]
Huh?
So, tell me, Iona, was it?
How much do you know about Mayu?
Here it comes!
Just so we're clear,
I wasn't the one
who told Fumio
about Mayu, you know.
She knew before we even met,
about her and the room
and everything else.
[CHIYORI]
Huh?!
[RUKO]
But how?
I wasn't always Fumio Futase.
Before this...
...I was an LRIG.
[ALL gasp]
You... used to be an LRIG?
[YUZUKI]
But you became a human.
You won the game.
Why would you wanna
be a Selector?
Is there something
we don't know?
It was for her, my Selector.
[FUMIO]
I did it to fulfill her wish.
And Fumio isn't my name.
It's hers.
But all of you know
how that works.
Although we are apart now,
we are as bound by her
wish as the day we met.
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL)]
You can... move around?
[LRIG] You're watching me
do it, aren't you?
And you can talk, too--
just like a real girl.
[LRIG]
Kinda goes without saying.
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL)]
Huh...?
[LRIG]
Actually.
You don't seem too surprised.
You're more like "Oh, hey,
it's a talking card,
don't see that
every day, huh?"
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL)] Hmph.
I read a lot of fantasy books.
Maybe I've been conditioned.
[LRIG]
Hmm...
I guess I still need
to introduce myself.
You can call me Fumio.
What's your name?
[LRIG]
I can't really remember.
Call me whatever you want.
I see.
Then from now on,
your name's "Futase."
[FUMIO]
Whoever I was before was lost.
For me, this was a new name
and a new beginning.
[FUTASE] You click and click and
click on that thing every day.
Is it really that much fun?
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL) sighs]
Not really...
Not right now at least.
The story isn't coming together,
so it's just frustrating.
[FUTASE]
Then why don't you quit?
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL) sighs] Because
it's really fun, sometimes, too.
I love when I feel a real
sense of accomplishment.
[FUTASE]
Hm?
Don't you have something that's
worth struggling for, Futase?
Not really.
If you mean like a wish,
or whatever?
I try my best not to think
about that kinda stuff.
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL)]
Sounds like something bad
happened to you in the past.
[FUTASE sighs]
So, I won't
pressure you about it.
If you ever decide you
wanna talk, I'm here, though.
I don't get it.
Why don't you ever look for
other Selectors to battle?
It's complicated.
[FUMIO] No matter how
many times I asked her,
I could never get her
to battle, even once.
[SELECTOR A]
Huh?
What do mean you don't want to?
Nothing personal, but I
have to achieve my dream
with my own two hands.
Otherwise, there's no point.
[SELECTOR A] Hmph!
Whatever, you little snob!
[FUMIO]
Of course, she was lying.
If her wish was
something so simple,
then an LRIG wouldn't
have appeared before her
in the first place.
I'll see you later.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[GIRL A] And then,
the guy lost his shirt!
[GIRLS B, C giggle]
[GIRL D]
No way!
Like anyone's
gonna believe that!
[GIRL F] It's true!
I can show you the pictures!
[GIRL D]
Whoops! We're gonna be late!
[GIRL E]
Dang it, not again!
[GIRL F] Remind me to
tell you the rest after class!
[GIRL E] Go! Go! Go!
I don't want detention!
[GIRL I]
Is that a new card?
I want one!
[GIRL G]
Well, this one's mine!
And I'm about to
school you with it!
[GIRL I]
Show me what you got!
[GIRL H]
I play winner, okay?
[FUTASE]
You bought a WIXOSS deck.
You could be playing
with the other girls.
I guess so.
You might have noticed that
I'm not the best at socializing.
[FUTASE]
Going to school day after day
and never talking
to anyone, though?
That's gotta be hell.
I'm used to it.
[FUTASE] You can't
enjoy living like that.
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL) sighs]
Actually, things are a lot
better lately, with you around.
Wha...? Really?
Of course.
Even you're smiling now.
[FUTASE giggles]
I guess it's contagious!
[FUMIO]
When I became an LRIG,
I lost everything, so it was
easy to become fixated on that.
But as time passed,
things changed.
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL) chuckles]
[FUMIO]
Before I knew it.
I became as invested
in her wish as she was.
But then--
[door slams]
[FUMIO'S MOM]
Another overnighter?!
You think I don't know
what's going on?!
[FUMIO'S DAD]
What?! I was working!
[FUMIO'S MOM] You wanna stop
being an ass and settle this?!
[FUMIO'S DAD]
Sure!
Soon as you wanna
talk about the guy
you're screwing behind my back!
--[glass shatters]
--[FUMIO (ORIGINAL) whimpers]
[FUMIO'S MOM yelps]
[FUMIO] Although she
tried to block it out,
bit by bit, reality
gnawed away at her dream,
and her one hope of escape
became yet another
source of pain.
[SELECTOR A]
You again?
Listen, I'm here to win,
not to have fun.
If you don't wanna battle
for real, beat it.
The situation has changed--I'm
ready when you are.
[FUTASE]
Fumio...?
[SELECTOR A] Oh yeah?
You shoulda said so sooner!
Are you sure about this?
You can still make your wish
happen on your own
if you keep fighting for it!
Maybe I can and maybe I can't,
but I'm fed up with this.
I thought I could
do things my way,
but I'm just not strong enough.
If we can't make
my dream come true,
there's no point
in living anymore.
[gasps]
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL)]
I can't do this alone...
I need you...
[FUTASE]
Then I'm here.
I'll fight and fight
for your wish
with every ounce of my being.
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL)]
Thank you, Futase...
I'm your LRIG, you know.
That's what I was born to do.
Well, let's start the show.
Open!
[FUMIO] Her initial reluctance
was completely cast aside.
She was an exceptional Selector.
Always one step ahead
of her opponent,
unrelenting in the
pursuit of her wish.
And in the end...
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL), FUTASE] I now
accept The Laws of the Selector
which state that with
this sacred oath
a new Eternal Girl
will now be born.
It's over?
I did my best and now
my wish comes true?
I'll keep my promise,
no matter what.
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL) gasps]
Futase...?
I'll fight for your wish with
every ounce of my being.
So please, don't worry.
[FUMIO (ORIGINAL)]
No. Wait.
What is this?!
[FUMIO] The girl who dreamed
of becoming a novelist
was trapped inside
a card instead.
[FUMIO]
The LRIG tasked with her wish
was carried down
the river of stars.
And soon, as those
who came before her,
floated to the room where
the girl of fate slept.
[MAYU]
Do you know the Girl of White?
So pure and innocent,
with a heart as warm
as the morning sun.
But there is a
Girl of Black as well.
Cruel and wicked, with a heart
as cold as the darkest night.
[gasps]
She burns with jealousy.
Resenting every shining smile
that dances upon the cheeks
of the Girl of White.
And eventually...
...that bitter hatred turns
to thoughts of erasing
her very existence.
You think... all of that's true?
I sense something strange
coming from your LRIG.
She's unlike the others.
Tell me, Iona.
Are you her?
Are you the Girl of Black?
[ALL gasp]
[RUKO]
Wha-What do you mean?
[MAYU]
Don't do it, Iona.
Can't you see it's wrong?
[MAYU]
You're the Girl of Black.
You can't dream of
becoming the Girl of White.
The light is not yours.
It will stain you.
As gray as ash!
[MAYU]
The Girl of Black.
The Girl of Darkness.
Do you want to hear a secret?
[RUKO] Next time:
"That Existence is Dark Black."