[AKIRA giggling]
[AKIRA] So, girls...
What do you think about
this new face of mine?
Be honest--
Pretty hideous, isn't it?
Pretty sad, isn't it?
[AKIRA giggles]
Pretty ironic, isn't it?
My wish was to
ruin Iona's career.
But the only thing
that got ruined was my face.
It was my intention
to end her modeling career.
But it happened to me instead.
Freaking insane, isn't it?
[crazed giggling]
[AKIRA]
C'mon, it's funny, isn't it?
[crazed giggling]
[AKIRA] You should be laughing!
[AKIRA]
So...
--[AKIRA] Laugh, damn it!
--[YUZUKI] Ruko!
[AKIRA] I used to be super-cute,
but now look
at what I've become!
Guess I'm not too
Aki-lucky anymore, am I?
C'mon! Look!
I'm a freaking mess!
[YUZUKI] Back off, Akira!
[AKIRA] This is all your fault.
[RUKO] What?
[AKIRA] I lost to you.
[AKIRA] And now I'm all alone
with this jacked-up face.
Let's fix that.
[AKIRA] You and you and Iona.
I'm gonna carve all your faces
up so you look just like me!
[POLICE OFFICER A]
What are you kids doing here?
[POLICE OFFICER A] Hold up!
Stay right there, you two!
Ruko! Let's book it!
Uh, right!
[YUZUKI] She kept her memories.
[RUKO] Uh... Yeah.
[YUZUKI] Then we're good.
[RUKO] No, we're not.
This is awful.
Akira's right about
the stuff she said.
Her wish getting
corrupted is my fault!
Ruko.
[YUZUKI] Look,
you still don't have a wish.
You should quit now
while you're ahead.
[RUKO] Wha--?
Really.
If something bad happens,
think about what it
would do to your grandma.
The same thing goes
for you, too, Yuzuki!
Think about how
your parents would feel
if something happened to you!
And Kazuki!
He'd be heartbroken,
wouldn't he?
[YUZUKI] I can't quit.
You have to!
C'mon, you saw what
losing did to Akira!
[YUZUKI]
I won't end up like her.
Yeah, but you don't know that!
[YUZUKI] Ruko.
It's sweet of you
to worry, it is.
No, please.
I have to keep pushing,
just a little more.
I've come way too far
to give up on my dream now.
And I'm this close
to making it happen.
So--God, I hate this--
We can't be friends anymore.
No matter what, I'm
going to be an Eternal Girl.
If you keep
hanging around with me,
our friendship could
be used against you,
and I don't
want you to suffer.
[RUKO] No, wait!
[YUZUKI] I'm sorry.
Yuzuki! Please, don't go!
[YUZUKI] Ruko!
[YUZUKI] It was really
fun being your friend!
Our matching scrunchies?
I will treasure that forever!
Then why...?
Next time we meet,
I'll be a new me!
No more regrets!
I'll finally be Kazuki's
girlfriend for real!
[TAMA] Hey... Ru?
[TAMA] Ru?
Ruko!
Call home if
you're gonna be late!
And where in the world have
you been all this time, anyway?
[RUKO] None of your business.
[slap lands]
Fine, so it's not
my business or whatever.
But still, you shouldn't
worry Grandma like that.
It's not cool.
You okay?
Is she--
Is she home?
Yeah.
Go let her know
you're all right.
Hi. Sorry.
[HATSU] Oh, thank
goodness you're home!
Cold cold, go away!
[HATSU] Lucky for you
I made some hot cider.
I had a feeling you'd be cold
after walking
outside for so long!
Don't just stand there!
Grandma...
Why aren't you asking me
questions about where I've been?
Because, dear, I know
when you're ready to talk...
...you'll let me know.
Sound good to you?
[RUKO sobbing]
[TAMA] Ru?
Did the hot cider taste yummy?
[TAMA] Are you asleep?
I wish you were awake
and having a battle
'cause I like seeing
how much fun you have.
But you know...
[TAMA] There's one thing
that I don't like.
Seeing you sad.
[KAZUKI yawning]
[YUZUKI] Morning, Kazuki!
[KAZUKI] Whoa, you made this?
[YUZUKI] Yep, sure did!
And by some miracle, I didn't
even burn down the house!
Here, I made soup, too!
[KAZUKI] Thank goodness.
[YUZUKI] For soup?
No, that you finally
came out of your room
after last night.
I worried about you.
[YUZUKI]
Girls have days like that,
so the best thing to do is
steer clear and leave 'em be.
Yeah, say no more.
[YUZUKI] Good, now eat.
Right. And thanks for cooking.
It's good!
The last time you
made French toast,
it was a real
disaster, remember?
Yeah.
I used to rush things
way too much.
Lose my cool and mess up.
No more of that!
'Cause I've learned
to calm down.
Take my time and set my sights.
That way everything
works out in the end, right?
I guess so.
[YUZUKI] Seeing some friends?
[KAZUKI] Oh, yeah.
I won't be gone for too long.
Well, that's good.
'Cause I'm making
dinner tonight.
Really?
I wonder what
we should have?
We had French toast for
breakfast, so for dinner...
--Curry udon!
Yeah, that's right, Kazuki,
I know you better
than you know yourself!
[KAZUKI] Well...
Gotta jet.
Cool, have a good time!
[YUZUKI] Hitoe. I'm sorry,
but I can't do it.
I can't lose and
end up like you did.
[YUZUKI] I'm gonna make
my wish come true.
[MALE SHOPKEEPER A] Morning.
[SELECTOR B] Hey.
Did you write that?
[SELECTOR B] Not trying
to get on your case,
but isn't it kinda dangerous
to find opponents like that?
[YUZUKI] Yeah, I dunno,
you're probably right.
[SELECTOR B] Look, personally,
I don't have a problem with it,
but I could see where
other Selectors would.
Even my LRIG thinks
it's kinda sketchy.
[YUZUKI] Well...
[YUZUKI] I can't wait for
opponents to come find me.
I need to get this
thing done already.
Huh?
'Cause I'm so close.
After I beat you,
my wish will come true.
Wow, pretty
confident, aren't you?
All right, then.
Let's do this.
--Open!
Something tells me
today's the day.
I don't know what
it is, but I feel different.
I think it's
the end of the road.
Perhaps so.
Hanayo! Get ready!
This girl is crazy serious.
[YUZUKI] It's not wrong.
It never was.
I don't care
what people think.
[YUZUKI] The bond we have...
[HONOKA] When I see you
stalking him all day,
it just makes me
feel sorry for him.
[YUZUKI] The love I feel...
[AKIRA] That is super-duper
naughty--You dirty girl!
Spell!
Fissure of Condemnation!
[YUZUKI] Direct Damage!
[YUZUKI] I'm not wrong.
[YUZUKI] I can change it all.
[YUZUKI]
No matter what it takes,
I won't let this world
deny my feelings anymore!
[YUZUKI] In the end...
...Kazuki will be mine!
[HANAYO] Understood!
[BOY 6B] Crap!
Dude, you beat me!
Wow, you're so good, Kazuki!
[BOY 8A]
Good? He's the best!
[BOY 8A] Now it's my turn
and you're goin' down!
[BOY 6B]
No way I'm losing to you!
Hey, so can you
take a look at my deck?
Sure thing.
Oh, you're gonna use Red?
Yep.
'Cause I think the
gem-themed SIGNI is so cute.
Yuzuki thinks so, too.
You know,
I'm a little thirsty.
Hey, um...
If I get juice,
can I bring it in here?
Oh. Yeah, of course.
[HONOKA]
Kazuki, will you come with?
[KAZUKI] Hey, wait...
What about--
No, over here.
[KAZUKI]
Huh?
[HONOKA]
Sorry I had to trick you.
I just said the
whole juice thing
because I couldn't think of
a better way to get you alone.
Do you think...
...we could go out together?
Um, look...
I do like you, Honoka,
but just not in that way.
Sorry...
Because there's
somebody else, right?
No, there's
nobody else, I swear.
[HONOKA] Are you sure?
What about Yuzuki?
It's not because of her?
You two are
always together,
so you can't blame
people for thinking it.
We all know!
[KAZUKI] Wait!
You all know what?
What are people thinking?
Duh, that you and Yuzuki
are like, "doing stuff!"
[HONOKA] Everyone says you are.
You didn't know?
Who the hell is "everyone?"
I mean, that's so messed up!
Who'd even say
that kind of sicko crap?
Tell me!
How could you think
such a thing about Yuzuki?
So who was it? Tell me!
Matsumoto?
Or Senda?
Give me some names now!
I'll go set 'em straight!
Well, if the
rumors aren't true,
why are you so upset over
what people say about you guys?
Drop it!
If I'm wrong about
your weird relationship,
then prove it!
Uh, prove it how?
Kiss me.
Huh?
Why do I have to do that?
Well, since I
bared my soul to you,
the least you could
do is give me a kiss!
If you're single and
not doing something weird
with your sister,
what's the harm?
Am I right?
This is insane.
No, Kazuki, wait!
[YUZUKI] Something...
is definitely different.
Summon Cannon and with
its effect, banish Lotus!
[SELECTOR B screams]
[YUZUKI] I don't feel like
I have a fever or anything,
but I'm burning up inside.
Is this a sign
that maybe my wish...
It will come true.
At last.
Yuzuki, listen to me.
I'm going to ask one last time.
Yeah, what is it?
[HANAYO] You are correct.
If you do win this battle, your
fondest wish will come true.
[HANAYO]
Are you sure about this?
When I saw
what Hitoe became,
I was mad that you
kept me in the dark.
But still...
Even if you had told
me what could happen
right from the
very beginning,
I would have wanted
to keep on fighting.
I don't care what it might take.
I'll become an Eternal Girl
at any cost!
Now, attack with Eagle! Go!
[YUZUKI] Right.
I've gotta do this for my wish.
I feel really bad about
what happened to Hitoe.
But...
Her wish was something
that could come true
without being a Selector.
[YUZUKI] But mine?
There's nothing I can do.
People will always frown on it.
I need power.
I need a miracle.
[HANAYO] Yuzuki.
Since you've
made your decision,
let us join together
for one final attack.
Now, the oath.
Do you remember it?
Yeah, it's... uh...
"I accept..."
"...the laws of the Selector."
"I accept the laws
of the Selector."
And, um...
"And upon this sacred oath,
a new Eternal Girl
shall be born!"
[HANAYO, YUZUKI]
Adamasphere!
[SELECTOR B screaming]
[YUZUKI] Is this...?
[HANAYO] It is the birth
of a new Eternal Girl.
[YUZUKI]
Wait...
What's happening?
[YUZUKI screaming]
[HATSU] It's your
day off from school, Ru.
Wouldn't you rather
be playing your card game?
[RUKO] Mm, nah.
[RUKO] I always have
a good time with you,
no matter what
we do. And besides...
...WIXOSS battles
might be fun, but...
after seeing all
the pain they cause...
I... I...
We can't be friends anymore.
What is it?
[RUKO] Nothing!
Just trying to swallow a hiccup!
All right.
[RUKO] I have to stay away
from those cards!
[phone vibrating]
Hello?
[BOY 8A] Dude, why did
you take off like that?
Honoka's pretty ticked.
She said you
treated her like crap!
You gotta apologize!
I'll help you
smooth things over,
but get back here right--
Why are girls
such drama queens?
[KAZUKI] Yuzuki's not like that.
She's always smiling.
And honest, too.
Even if she's upset.
She tries to keep it to herself.
[HONOKA] Duh, that you and
Yuzuki are like, "doing stuff!"
[KAZUKI] No, that's crazy!
Hey, I'm home.
[tumbling noise]
Yuzuki? What happened?
[HANAYO'S voice] Just got
dizzy for a moment.
Sorry. I'll be fine.
Look, you better lie down.
Can you walk?
[HANAYO (Y)]
Thank you, Kazuki.
No problem.
Did you put something on?
What?
[KAZUKI] Like perfume?
You smell nice.
You know, they say if you
like someone's natural smell,
that person is
the love of your life.
I didn't come up
with the idea.
Just saying, that's all.
C'mon, what are
you talking about?
If you're trying
to make me laugh,
this is just kinda awkward!
Even if you like your family,
the "love of your life"
is someone else.
[HANAYO (Y)]
And if I was someone else?
[KAZUKI] Other than my twin?
We were born as
two halves of one whole,
so in order for
us to be complete...
...maybe we just
need to be together.
Something's not right.
[HANAYO (Y)] With who?
[KAZUKI] You.
My friends.
Did someone say
something to you?
You can talk to me
about anything.
All right?
Kazuki...
I'm yours if you need me.
[HANAYO (Y)] Now and forever.
[knocking]
[HITOE'S MOTHER] Can I come in?
[HITOE'S MOTHER] Hitoe?
Did you eat, dear?
No, not even the
lunch I brought you?
Sweetie, you have
to eat something.
Oh, before I forget,
I got a little
gift for you.
Take a look.
[HITOE gasps]
[HITOE'S MOTHER] You like
this game, don't you?
I saw an ad about
a new WIXOSS deck
being released, so I thought
I'd get you one to cheer you up.
Why don't you flip through it
and see what you got?
Oh, I bought a cake, also.
Tell you what, I'm gonna bring
up a big ol' slice for you,
okay?
Be right back.
[choked sob]
[HITOE sobbing]
[HITOE gasps]
Nice to meet you...
...Selector.
[YUZUKI] A card game?
[KAZUKI]
Wait, the card did what now?
[RUKO] A wish.
[KAZUKI] I assume you're the one
responsible for all of this?
[YUZUKI]
Thank you for that, Hanayo.
[RUKO] Wait a minute,
does this mean
you're all better now
and you remember me?
[RUKO] Next time:
"The Cruel Truth."