[NEWS ANNOUNCER (F)] It looks
to be a wet one tomorrow
with scattered showers
throughout the day...
[HATSU] Suppose I won't
be hanging anything
outside to dry tomorrow.
[RUKO] Grandma, I'm home!
Oh, hi, want a snack?
There's something
I gotta check first!
Sure, no hurry.
[YUZUKI] Oh, come on!
Why are you so slow?
I'm not used to
Ayumu's laptop!
Here we go...
[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO] Whoa...
Holy crap!
Iona really is trying to gather
all the Selectors together!
It's happening
really close to here, too.
[YUZUKI] Around here, huh?
[RUKO] Yeah.
[YUZUKI] Ruko?
This is...
[HATSU] They're only one
building away from a Tetris.
And then the whole city
might just disappear on us.
[TAMA] Ru?
[RUKO gasps]
[TAMA] Is something wrong?
Huh-uh. Not at all.
[TAMA groans]
Ruko, listen...
If something's
bothering you,
or if you've got something
on your mind, say it.
Yuzuki...
Is it... true?
Am I scary?
'Cause people say they
never know what I'm thinking.
Huh?
No, that wasn't what
I was trying to say before!
I meant you try to figure
things out all on your own,
and hold everything inside.
Uhhh... You know,
kinda like I do?
I'm sorry, okay?
Still friends, right?
Like back when we bought these?
'Course we are...
You're one of the kindest
people I've ever known.
What? Hey!
Come on, knock it off!
You're making me blush.
Turns out you're
also one of the strongest.
Ru?
I wish...
I could be like that...
Yuzuki... Tama... I'm sorry.
I've decided
to battle Iona.
[TAMA gasps]
Wha... What are
you talking about?
I thought you said
you gave up battling!
[RUKO] Yeah... I did.
Huh...?
The thing is...
Now, I have
a wish to fight for!
It's... a good one.
It's to save you. You and Tama!
Plus everyone else
who became LRIGs!
I swear! I'll bring
you all back to normal!
I'll get you out
of this crazy game.
I don't care what I
have to sacrifice to do it.
That's my one and only wish!
Oh, Ru...
That's sweet, but
it can't be done. Sorry.
Wha--? Why not?
'Cause like me, every LRIG
used to be a normal girl.
And the LRIGs who
replace winning Selectors
become normal girls again.
Even though
they're bound by an oath
to fulfill your wish, there's
a limit to what they can do.
So you're telling me
there are some wishes
that can never come true?
Like going back in time
or reshaping reality?
[MAYU] That's correct.
[YUZUKI gasps]
[MAYU] But it's not
my place to decide
which are possible
and which are not.
[YUZUKI] What?
[MAYU] Most wishes can come true
thanks to the
efforts of the LRIG.
Assuming, of course, that she
upholds her end of the oath.
Whether it's due to personal
morality, common sense,
or simply a matter
self-preservation,
an LRIG may become reluctant.
But she must cast
these feelings aside,
and prioritize the Selector's
wish above her own life.
If an LRIG refuses the wish...
...she will remain
trapped in her card,
unable to return
to the outside world.
Therefore, to
guarantee both the wish
and her eventual
escape from her card.
From the moment they meet,
she must do anything
and everything to
reach that conclusion.
Even deceiving her Selector.
That's why...
[MAYU] Otherwise,
you wouldn't agree
to the ritual of
acknowledgement.
It's a catalyst, you see, a
trigger for the transformation.
[HANAYO] Now... the oath.
Do you remember it?
Yeah. It's, uh...
"I accept."
"The laws of the Selector."
"I accept the laws of
the Selector." And, um...
[BOTH] "And upon
this sacred oath,
a new Eternal Girl
shall be born!"
[MAYU] Once an Eternal Girl,
she is obligated
to fulfill the wish
that has been made.
Though she may
have deceived you,
she has entered a contract
that cannot be broken.
For if she fails
to uphold her end.
The Eternal Girl
will disappear.
[YUZUKI] Remember
what Hanayo said?
[YUZUKI] About how you couldn't
wish Hitoe's memories back?
That probably
means you can't just
"undo" things with another wish.
Yeah, but those girls,
the ones who are LRIGs.
I have no idea
how to get them out,
or if it's even possible,
but, this Mayu girl...
The one in that
weird white room.
She might. I just
don't know how to
get back to that
place to ask her.
Maybe I can get 'em out.
[RUKO] Huh?
I'm not sure why,
but somewhere deep down,
I feel like I might know how.
I think I might be able to turn
all the LRIGs back to normal.
Wha...?!
You really think so?
Yeah, kinda!
But there's this feeling,
something inside saying
"Yes. I can do this thing."
Well, maybe...
Tama...
Makes me wonder...
Uh?
[YUZUKI] No, that's crazy...
[YUZUKI] If the Eternal Girls
have so little power,
what's the point
in going through
all this mess
in the first place?
We're stuck in a card,
and they die if they
can't fulfill the wish!
If we couldn't make
the wish come true
and they're us now, then
aren't you condemning us all?!
[MAYU] There are exceptions.
[YUZUKI gasps]
[MAYU] That is to say,
some Eternal Girls
are more... "special"
than others...
You may lack
the power to create
this fairy tale
ending you so desire,
but there is magic
yet in this world.
[YUZUKI] You expect
me to buy into
some fantasy
mumbo-jumbo like that?
[MAYU] Given what you
have just been through,
I'm surprised you would deny
the very concept so flippantly.
And now it seems
the time has come.
[MAYU] Morning dawns
on your life as an LRIG.
You now go to
meet your Selector.
No, wait! Tell me who you are!
[glass shatters]
[YUZUKI grunts]
[YUZUKI screams]
[MAYU] I'm the one who
will always be here.
In the rift that exists
between the world of the cards,
and the world of reality.
Good luck. And goodbye.
[YUZUKI screams]
You know,
Tama does seem
awfully different
from other LRIGs.
Maybe she's one of those
so-called "special" ones.
So... maybe my
wish can come true!
[YUZUKI] No dice.
Wha--?
Remember, if you
take the oath,
you're just gonna turn
into an LRIG like I did!
[TAMA gasps]
Right. But still...
Since my wish is to release
all the LRIGs from their cards
and make them real again,
maybe that means I won't
be able to become one.
[YUZUKI] Are you nuts?!
For all you know,
we could get fixed
while you're stuck
as an LRIG forever!
Or, God forbid, something worse!
I know, but I--
[YUZUKI] Ruko, please, you've
gotta give this more thought.
I mean, sure, if you're a card,
maybe I could find you.
And maybe we could be
friends like we are now.
But, people
who aren't Selectors,
like your grandmother
and brother...
They'll never see you again!
[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO] Hitoe...?
Sorry, but I'd like
my LRIG back now.
[RUKO] Hitoe, look, I, uh...
[HITOE] I don't care,
just give her back, okay?
[YUZUKI] Hitoe!
[YUZUKI] Hold on,
w-we need to talk!
Yeah. Calm down.
It's cool. I just--
I don't want to hear it
and I have nothing
to say to you.
Hitoe!
No, wait!
[RUKO gasps]
[HITOE'S MOTHER] Hitoe?
I'm taking my LRIG
and I'm going to compete
in Iona's fan event.
[RUKO gasps]
If you want to
talk to me so badly,
you can do it
on the battlefield.
[RUKO] If my wish comes true,
I might never see Grandma again.
[elevator dings]
[RUKO] What should I do?
Grandma, I'm--
[HATSU] Oh. Hello.
Yes, she's fine.
[HATSU] She's even made friends.
Mm-hmm, she sure did.
[HATSU] What's that?
There's no point blaming
yourself for this.
Not anymore.
I'm tired of hearing it.
This has all been
settled before.
And I won't
have you pretending
to be her mother, either.
I don't hold a
thing against you,
but when you said you
weren't meant to be a parent,
I was inclined to agree,
and my opinion hasn't changed.
Remember, I love
having the kids here.
Ayumu and Ruko
are both utter joys.
They always brighten my day.
[floorboards creak]
Yes. Right. Okay,
I'll call you then.
You take care now.
Hi, Ru. You about
ready for dinner?
[RUKO] Was that Mom?
Guess what?
I finally thought of a wish.
Oh, is that so?
Uh-huh.
Y'see, when I was little,
Mom and Dad were
supposed to be close
but all they did was fight.
It made me sad.
It made me think if you
got close to someone,
you'd just end up getting hurt,
so I stayed away from people.
Well, except for you
and Ayumu, of course.
I didn't think I needed
anyone else but you guys.
But over the last
few weeks, that's changed.
I've actually made
some true friends,
and they're real
important to me, too.
And it's because
of them that, well...
You were telling
me the other day
you hoped you could do
something for your friends.
Is this wish of yours for them?
[HATSU] It's not something bad?
No, of course not,
I mean--!
[HATSU] So it's
something good, then?
Well, yeah. I think it is.
It kinda has to be.
You have a
good heart, Ru.
And you believe
your wish is good.
The very fact that you wished
it for your friends instead of
for yourself proves to me you're
probably on the right track.
So you do what
you need to, dear.
And I'm sure it will come true.
Your friends are very lucky
to have you and so am I.
Grandma!
[HATSU] Aw, it's all right,
there's no reason to cry.
[RUKO sobs]
[RUKO grunts]
[TAMA] Ru?
[RUKO] Huh?
[TAMA] So you're...
gonna battle?
[RUKO] Mm-hmm!
We're gonna take on
that mean girl Iona again.
I bet you can't wait!
[TAMA] No! I don't want to!
Huh?
Your Grandma doesn't
know what could happen!
If she did, she wouldn't
have said all that.
She wouldn't let
you risk your life!
I don't care if I'm stuck
in this dumb card forever.
It's better than being alone!
You may never see me
or your Grandma again!
So please don't do this, Ru,
I don't want to lose you!
But Tama, I'm sure
my plan is gonna work.
[TAMA] But Yuzuki
said it might not!
Then what'll happen?
I'm sorry,
but I've gotta do this.
I won't become an LRIG
and I won't let you stay one.
I promise...
we'll never be apart.
[TAMA gasps]
Really.
You and I will do
everything together.
[RUKO] Have yummy
breakfasts with Grandma...
[RUKO] Run so we're
not late to school...
Hang out with
Yuzuki and Hitoe...
We'll all be best friends.
It's closed now,
but during the summer
we'll go to the candy
shop on the corner.
They've got this ice cream
you wouldn't believe.
We'll try a new
flavor every day!
Trust me. You'll love it.
So, sound good?
[TAMA] It does, but no.
[RUKO gasps]
Don't do it...
[RUKO sighs]
[RUKO] I'm sorry, Tama...
I am... But...
I have to finish this.
[HATSU]
Be careful now, okay, Ru?
[RUKO] Okay.
[HATSU] Think you'll be
home in time for dinner?
Good question...
[RUKO] I'll try.
And do you think we could
have potatoes au gratin?
With lots of bacon
the way you like?
[RUKO] Oh, please!
Love you, Grandma.
[RUKO] All right. Here goes...
[RUKO] Oh, wow. These girls...
All of 'em are Selectors here
to fight for their wishes...
[RUKO gasps]
[TV static crackles]
[SELECTORS gasp]
[IONA] Ladies.
Welcome to the fan event.
Rather, welcome to the
Selectors-only WIXOSS party.
This building is
owned by my Father
and the work crews
are off today.
So we don't have to worry
about being disturbed.
We've all been battling
to make our wishes come true.
And yet, we don't
know how many wins
we need to make that happen.
Frustrating, isn't it?
I started to wonder:
What if there was something
we could do to change that?
Hence this party.
With so many Selectors
gathered to do battle,
some are bound
to win enough
to meet these
elusive conditions.
As a result, a large
number of Eternal Girls
will be born right here today.
These Selectors...
They have no clue.
[IONA] Now, obviously,
for each of you who wins,
there will be another who loses.
Speaking personally, I have
no desire to fight anyone
but the strongest
Selectors available.
[RUKO gasps]
Therefore,
I have assigned you all
to tournament brackets.
If you win a battle, you
progress to the next round.
If you lose, you're out.
This will at least
prevent multiple losses.
And the Selector who makes
it all the way to the top?
Well, you'll be
facing me, of course.
[RUKO] Twelfth floor...
Room four?
[IONA] Is everyone ready?
I hope so.
Because the
battle begins now.
[SELECTORS] Open!
Tama, Grow!
Gothic Boundary!
[TAMA grunts]
[SELECTOR C screams]
I know it hurts,
but when I'm finished,
none of you will ever have
to go through this again!
Summon: Mitsurugi!
This is the final blow, Tama!
Tama?
[TAMA yells]
[LRIG screams]
Tama...
[RUKO] Please, I need
you to agree to this.
Otherwise my wish
won't come true.
[RUKO] I'm sorry, Tama.
But we have to do it my way.
[RUKO] We have to keep battling.
I shoulda
seen this coming.
Guess so. You ready
to talk to me now?
Like I said:
on the battlefield.
[BOTH] Open!
No new Eternal Girls
have been born yet.
Not that I sense.
Oh well!
On the other hand,
it looks like some Selectors
are losing their third
and final battles.
I will find my way there.
To that white room
where she's waiting.
[RUKO] Bounce Sevieria,
and attack!
[HITOE grunts]
[TAMA growls]
[YUZUKI grunts]
Yuzuki! Grow now!
And banish Mikagami!
[TAMA grunts]
Dang it. She's so much
better than before.
Splitting Conviction.
[YUZUKI] Tama! Sorry!
[TAMA screams]
[HITOE gasps]
[HITOE] Yuzuki, attack!
Banish Square!
Hitoe...
It's wrong...
It's all wrong.
What do you
mean, "wrong"?
[RUKO] It's not supposed
to be like this.
Why can't you
remember how it was
when we played before?
Ruko...
[RUKO] We used to play
for fun, not to win.
No LRIGs, no battles, no wishes.
Back then, I thought
that wasn't enough.
I wanted serious battles--
serious victories,
instead of just
appreciating what I had.
Me, too...
[RUKO] Now it's gone.
We can never just enjoy
playing games again, as friends.
And I hate it...
[HITOE gasps]
I knew it.
Now she's sad too.
That means she must remember.
She still has memories of us.
[TAMA gasps]
You think?
Hitoe, listen!
Like Ruko said,
we all used to be friends!
What?
[HITOE screams]
No, stop!
Did that hurt?
I'm sorry, but I need
you to remember!
[HITOE whimpers]
[RUKO] Knock it off,
Yuzuki, you're hurting her!
[YUZUKI] I know, but do you
want her to stay like this?!
Her life being controlled
by these stupid battles?
I don't. I want to be
best friends like we were!
[RUKO] Me too! I don't
wanna battle like this!
I wanna do it as friends,
like we used to!
It was so much fun,
please remember!
No, please stop it,
this is killing me!
Hitoe! Remember!
Your wish to make
friends already came true!
You can quit all of this!
You still have us!
Stop it...
Stop it! Stop it!
[RUKO] You can do this, Hitoe!
Just remember how we used to be!
Would you please
just shut up?
[RUKO] Hitoe!
[HITOE] I don't want
to hear any more of this!
I just want to make my
wish come true, that's all!
Aren't you listening?!
I told you it already did! So...
[HITOE] Stop it!
[RUKO gasps]
[HITOE] No, okay?
This wasn't part of the deal!
You promised
we would battle
and you'd grant me a wish!
Wha-- I--
[YUZUKI gasps]
[RUKO] Her scrunchie...
She still has it!
[URITH] Now, then.
Ready to say goodbye?
I've waited
long enough already.
Soon I will face my
final battle as Iona Urazoe.
[URITH] Oh, one final note.
While it's been a
blast giving beatdowns
to other Selectors with you.
I'm not gonna miss you
one bit, you rotten bitch.
[URITH] Still, I'll be beside
you to the very end... Selector.
[RUKO] Next time:
"That Choice..."