[IONA] My favorite food?
Hmm. Strawberries... I guess.
[WRITER] I see! You have
cute tastes, Miss Iona.
[MALE STAFF A] Hate to say
"I told you so,"
but Akira's down
in the rankings again.
On top of that, she's
been ditching work lately.
She's really not
worth it anymore.
[MALE STAFF B] Eh, her
style doesn't really match
our magazine anyway.
Kinda "low-class," y'know?
[MALE STAFF A] So
what should we do
about the front page
model for the next issue?
What d'you think? Drop
Akira and go with Yuko?
[WRITER] Well,
that's just lovely.
I wish they'd have their little
business talk somewhere else.
I like them
with some milk.
And just a pinch of
sugar. Is that weird?
[WRITER] Huh? Oh, right,
strawberries. Sorry...
I always take the
backside of my fork.
And smash them to bits.
Just so we're clear,
I'm gonna make you apologize!
Open!
[HITOE] I'm home.
[HITOE'S MOTHER] My gosh!
What happened, Hitoe?
You're soaked
to the bone!
Your friends didn't come
with you? Did they go home?
[HITOE gasps]
Anyway, dry yourself
off before-- Hitoe?
Looks like I'm up
first! Aki-lucky!
We're gonna school
this scrub, Piriluk!
And don't go easy on her
just 'cause she's a newb!
Is it okay?
[RUKO] What?
Tama... will fight to win this.
Of course.
[TAMA gasps excitedly]
I'll draw. Drop a card in the
Ener Zone, have Piriluk, Grow!
And now, say hello to Sky Cat!
Tama. Let's Grow!
I summon Kukri and Ponya!
Tch! You gotta tell your
LRIG to lay off the coffee.
[TAMA giggles]
[RUKO] It's weird.
I've never felt like this.
But battling Akira
is awful. It's painful.
[RUKO] It is painful, but...
[RUKO] I love it!
What the hell? No fair!
I thought she was
supposed to be a newbie.
You are correct. Though
she's new to the game,
she takes battle
quite seriously.
Huh?
This is talent.
She has a gift.
You trying to tell
me something?
Why don't you turn around
and say it to my face? Huh?
You know what? Screw you,
I don't even care anymore!
You just keep your mouth shut
and do what I tell you, got it?
Let's get this crap
over with quick!
ARTS!
Time for
Peeping Analyze.
[RUKO gasps]
[AKIRA] Awww. Poor Ru-ru.
Now I get to pick a card level,
then all the ones in
your hand go bye-bye.
And since you dumb rookies
love to play by-the-book,
there's only one answer:
Level Four!
[RUKO screams]
Huh?
[PIRILUK] It would
seem you missed.
Arrgh! Who cares! I don't
need you to tell me that!
Why don't you do
something useful
and figure out her
wish for me instead?
My wish...
Here it comes!
Try not to flip out
and wet yourself when I see
your dirty little secret.
Hurry it up, Piriluk!
I haven't had my dose of
butt-hurt babies today.
There's nothing.
Huh? What's your deal?
You LRIGs can't like,
malfunction, can you?
She has...
no wish.
Yeah, she's right. I admit it.
I don't have a wish yet.
[AKIRA] Hah! What?
Lemme get this straight:
You're battling as a Selector,
but you have nothing
you wanna fight for?
That is, like, so messed up!
What are you, a
sociopath or something?
All the Selectors are,
like, do or die when it
comes to their wishes!
And you're just crapping all
over that so you can "have fun?"
That is sick, yo. Sick.
[IONA] Participating as a
Selector without having a wish
is more than just wrong.
It's blasphemy.
[RUKO] I don't
care what you say.
Huh?
[RUKO] Just means I
have nothing to lose!
So you can't scare me!
Arc Aura!
Tama!
[TAMA yells]
[RUKO yells]
[PIRILUK]
[AKIRA screams]
[AKIRA sobs]
[AKIRA] What the hell
is wrong with you...?
You just said you
don't have a wish.
So tell me:
Why the hell are you trying
to stomp all over mine?!
No, that's not
why I did this.
I just- wanted you to--
[AKIRA] Don't give me that crap!
You just wanted to see
me suffer, didn't you?
Ah, and I bet you enjoyed it!
[AKIRA sobs]
Hold on a sec!
[rain patters]
"Met with Ruko and Yuzuki.
Played WIXOSS at the library.
On our way back, we
bought stuffed dumplings."
Ruko and Yuzu--
[HITOE gasps in pain]
[HITOE gasps]
[HITOE screams]
Hitoe?!
[HITOE sobs]
[HITOE'S MOTHER] What happened?!
[HITOE] The words
are disappearing!
[HITOE'S MOTHER] What?
[HITOE] My notes!
Everything I wrote
is just fading away!
I don't know why!
I can't remember!
[HITOE cries]
Hitoe...
[MALE STAFF A]
Is Akira late again?!
Iona. Have you heard from her?
Not today.
[MALE STAFF A]
You know what? Forget it.
I don't even care anymore.
[MALE STAFF B] Right? She's
off the cover for next issue.
Good. Riddance.
Better yet, why don't we
just drop her for a while?
[MALE STAFF B] Sounds good.
[rain falls]
[AKIRA] Iona...
[giggles]
You have the scent
of battle on you.
Or the stink of
defeat, at least.
That reminds me.
Do you remember that poor girl
who battled Iona a while back?
That was her second battle
and her second defeat.
In other words, she
was one loss away from
bidding farewell to her wish.
Knowing that she was backed into
a corner, you approached her.
And you sweet-talked
her into another battle
with a free win as bait.
And as she sat there,
struggling to breathe,
suffering from the illness
that ravaged her body,
you betrayed her.
You crushed a dying girl
for your own gain.
It wasn't just her wish,
but her very life
that you snatched away from her.
[AKIRA] What does
it matter to you?!
I can run my battles however
the hell I want, can't I?!
Can't I?!
[URITH] Yes, you certainly can.
Though I do have to question
the effectiveness of your little
method, since you lost so badly
to the next girl Iona beat.
[URITH] That's why you stopped
feeding off Iona's scraps,
isn't it?
And why you started picking on
the rookie Selectors instead.
[URITH giggles]
[URITH] Tell me how that
worked out for you again?
[IONA] Yet another
loss. Pathetic.
I don't want your filthy
hands disgracing any more
Selector battles.
Screw you!
[URITH] Your wish is to see
Iona's life ruined, right?
[AKIRA gasps]
[URITH] I know you
want to beat her.
So why don't you challenge
her to a battle already?
Why do you avoid it
when she's right here?
I told you!
I can battle however
the hell I want to!
And either way, when I get
my wish you're going down!
[YUKO] Thank you very much!
[AKIRA] Huh...?
[URITH giggles]
[URITH] Oh! Looks like
Yuko's here for the shoot!
[AKIRA] Are you kidding?
But I thought me and Iona
were doing the cover today!
[IONA] You don't have
a shoot today. Sorry.
[AKIRA] What...?
While you were so occupied
looking for rookie Selectors
to pick on, you seem
to have lost your
coveted position as a model.
[AKIRA gasps]
[URITH laughs]
[URITH] Aw, are you gonna cry?
You tried too hard to ruin
Iona's career and
ended up ruining your own!
[IONA] I don't want
to keep them waiting.
[IONA] Goodbye, loser.
[AKIRA] I don't care about
my career, or my life,
or anything, as long
as I can ruin yours!
I'll tear you apart!
With my own two hands
if I have to, you bitch!
[URITH giggles]
[URITH] Time to put
her out of her misery.
[HATSU] It doesn't seem
like you have a fever...
But you're still
not feeling well?
No... My head feels
like it's gonna explode.
I see.
Well, I'll call the school for
you and tell them what's wrong.
You just lay there and
take it easy, all right?
Now I'm making
Grandma worry again.
[TAMA] Ru...
Ahh, and I bet
you enjoyed it!
Why do I like
battles so much?
Why do I keep
wanting to have them?
I know all the horrible
things that'll happen
if I continue playing.
But still... I can't stop!
You don't have to cry, Ru!
Y'know what?
It makes Tama so happy to
see you have fun battling!
So don't be sad! We can
have lots of battles and--!
No! Stop it!
Please, Ru...
[BOY A] Hey, Kazuki. You aren't
too busy today, are you?
[BOY B] Yeah, let's hang!
[KAZUKI laughs]
Okay! Sounds good!
[BOY A] Didn't think
you'd say yes.
[BOY B] Cool. We can
grab some grub.
[KAZUKI] If you like curry,
I know a place.
[BOY A] Let's go!
Can we talk for a sec?
[GIRL A] Nothing personal.
But you and Kazuki
are kinda leaving
a bad impression on people.
[YUZUKI] What?
[GIRL B] Like, the way
you two always hang out
is bordering on creepy.
Jeez, could you
be any more blunt?
Anyway, don't look so upset.
We're not teasing, we're
actually really worried.
You're worried?
[HONOKA] We've been hearing
all those awful rumors
about you two, so we came
to give you some advice.
Do you think I'm stupid?
What's it matter to you?
[sighs]
All right, fine, I'm
actually worried about Kazuki.
You, I couldn't care less about.
When I see you
stalking him all day.
It just makes me
feel sorry for him.
[GIRL A] Yeah, it's awkward!
Maybe you don't realize it,
but Kazuki's actually
a pretty popular guy.
But now there's all these
weird rumors because you--
Jeez, nice attitude.
[GIRL B] Guess what they
say about them is true. Ew.
[HONOKA] Now, now...
[YUZUKI] Damn it...
[HANAYO] Yuzuki.
[YUZUKI] Don't talk to me!
[YUZUKI] What's wrong with
them? Everyone's so stupid.
They're the creepy ones, not me.
[YOUNG GIRL] Howdy-dooo!
I knew it! You're a
Selector, aren't you?
Yay! I finally met one.
I am the awesomest!
Ugh! Selectors are
so hard to find!
Oh, by the way,
my name's Chiyori!
So can we have a battle
already? Pretty pretty please?
Listen, kid. Here's
a little secret.
[CHIYORI] Ooh!
If you lose three
Selector battles...
Something unspeakably
terrible happens to you.
Yuzuki...
Duh, I already knew that! It's
all written down, right here!
Huh? A novel? Of WIXOSS?
[CHIYORI] Yup! So yeah,
after your third loss,
the magical WIXOSS Factors
inside your body go crazy
and blow up like a hot air
balloon, until "kaboom!"
Guts flying everywhere!
Pretty scary!
Wait, that's not--
[CHIYORI] That's why
Selectors are so cool, right?
They put their lives on the
line to fight for their wishes!
Uh-huh...
[laughter]
Hey, sorry.
My girl here's a little soft
in the head, you see.
Ugh! Eldora!
She'll see how hard my
head is when we battle!
Now! Back to what I
was saying before!
I'm offering my commemorative
first battle to you,
Ms. Selector-on-the-playground!
I don't know...
[HONOKA laughing]
Oh, stop it. You're
too much, Kazuki!
It's not that
big a deal.
[HONOKA] You don't have
to go home yet, do you?
[KAZUKI] Uh, no, I guess not.
[HONOKA] Oh good! There's
still a bunch of stuff
I need to ask you!
[CHIYORI] C'mon, let's
battle! Please! For me?
[YUZUKI] Fine.
Yuzuki!
Let's do this.
Yay! Finally!
It's battle time!
[knock on door]
Hey, Sweetie, I've
gotta step out for a bit.
Try to take it easy, okay?
[HITOE] It's strange...
I feel like I've been
searching for something.
But I can't remember
what it is...
[bird chirping]
[HITOE] I just know
that if I can't have it...
Nothing matters...
And there's no reason
to be alive anymore.
[CHIYORI sobs]
[CHIYORI] The bitter,
bitter taste of defeat.
[ELDORA] Yep, she's strong.
Way stronger than you, Chiyori.
Sorry about that. Bet that was
a waste of your time, huh?
You're so rude!
Learn the rules!
In her first fight the
heroine has to lose, okay?
[ELDORA] Yeah, I'll be sure
to write that one down.
[CHIYORI] Oh! Here,
give this a read, it's good.
We'll meet again
for sure. Right?
Fare thee well,
Selector!
[CHIYORI grunts]
[CHIYORI makes engine noises]
You all right?
[YUZUKI] Well, I finally won.
[HANAYO] Yes...
[YUZUKI] All it takes
are three losses
and my wish is gone forever.
But there's no telling how
many times I have to win
if I want it to come true.
Isn't that the way it works?
[HANAYO] "Only when the
conditions are met."
"The conditions," huh?
That's kind of cryptic,
don't you think?
I'm sure you'll tell me
after it's too late.
All I've thought about is
winning, but now I wonder
what would happen if
my wish was corrupted?
[YUZUKI] Maybe Kazuki would
drift away from me?
No, it has to be
worse than that.
I bet he would end up hating
me and I'd never see him
again for the rest of my life.
He was with that girl.
I wonder where they went?
[HANAYO] Stop it.
Maybe they went to Momoka's
place to pick out cards.
I think his friends are
still new to the game.
That used to be "our thing"
we did together, you know?
[HANAYO] Yuzuki, listen to me.
[YUZUKI] Then maybe
they'll go to a movie
and stop by the
food court afterwards
to try out their new decks.
Then they'll get a snack
and exchange numbers.
Laugh and smile...
Walk home together.
Yuzuki!
I hate it.
If they're going to
take Kazuki away from me,
I'd rather just die now
and get it over with!
[HANAYO] No matter
how upset you may be,
you should never say
something like that.
You don't think I'm serious?
I hate you for lying to me.
But, I know, I know I need you
for my wish to come true.
I'm not stupid!
I know Akira made
a fool of me,
but I did beat that
new girl, no problem!
If I still have a shot at
becoming an Eternal Girl,
then my wish can come true!
Kazuki can be mine forever.
And he won't be
taken away from me!
[HANAYO] Listen. I am your
LRIG, through thick and thin.
I will always follow you.
Wherever fate take us.
[RUKO] When I was
living with Mom,
I don't think I asked for too
much. I wasn't spoiled.
She always wanted
to be left alone,
so I tried not to
bother her. But--
[RUKO'S MOTHER] I don't know
what Ruko's thinking.
There's something...
scary about her.
[RUKO] I never knew how or
why I was scaring my mom.
And that made me afraid, too.
But I'm fine as long as I have
Grandma and Ayumu with me.
And I try not to ask for
too much from them.
I don't want to scare anyone,
or bother anyone,
or hurt anyone ever
again. But now--
[TAMA] Y'know what?
It makes Tama so happy to
see you have fun battling!
[RUKO panting]
[RUKO] No! No, please!
[RUKO grunts]
[AKIRA] Where do you get
off acting like a victim?
You just wanted
to see me suffer.
And I bet you enjoyed
it, didn't you?
[RUKO gasps]
[HATSU] Ru. Wake up, Ru!
There's a phone call for you.
I explained that
you were asleep,
but apparently, it's
something important.
[RUKO] Wha...?
[door bell chimes]
[HITOE'S MOTHER] Oh!
[HITOE'S MOTHER] Sorry to
just call out of the blue.
Do you like parfaits?
I probably should've
asked before I ordered,
but I hope it's okay.
[RUKO] Uh, thanks.
Hitoe usually gets the
kind with candied chestnuts.
This one looks awfully good.
I'll have to come back
here with her some time.
So what did you--
I looked through
Hitoe's phone.
She had your number and
Yuzuki's in her contacts.
[RUKO] Huh?
You must think I'm a
horrible mother for snooping,
but I also found this.
Here.
Hold on. Is this the notebook
she kept on WIXOSS?
You've seen it?
Uh, yes ma'am.
[HITOE'S MOTHER] Hitoe
can't read it anymore.
She said that all the
words were "disappearing."
She also tells me she
doesn't remember you.
[RUKO gasps]
[HITOE] Today, Ruko
and Yuzuki and I
bought a matching
set of scrunchies.
They both looked
really cute
when they put them in their
hair. They said I was cute too!
I'll have to take
their word for it.
I was already so happy,
but having the chance
to be together with them,
sharing all of our fun and
joy, it was just wonderful.
Friendship truly is
a beautiful thing.
[RUKO whimpers]
[HITOE'S MOTHER] She was so
happy to make new friends.
She wouldn't stop
talking about you.
I don't know what went wrong.
Ruko, please, if there's
anything you can tell me
about what happened,
even if you had an argument
or she got angry at you over
something, I don't care!
I promise I'm not trying to
blame you, but it seems like
something just snapped and I
need to know what caused it--!
[RUKO sobs]
Ruko... Tell me.
[RUKO whimpers]
[RUKO] Hitoe lost three times.
[HITOE'S MOTHER gasps]
[RUKO] I was just having fun,
battling with my friends.
We didn't know what
would happen if we lost.
I mean, her wish had
already come true.
We didn't know it would
get corrupted like that.
Ruko, I don't... Please, just
explain what this is about.
Ruko, wait!
[RUKO] I feel so lost.
Everything is wrong.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Help me!
[URITH] You came here because
you wanted to battle.
[RUKO] Why are you
saying this stuff?
[IONA] I want nothing
more than to battle you.
[RUKO] I do.
[URITH] Forget it
and have some fun!
[RUKO] Next time:
"The Girl's Desire."