[HITOE]
Chiyori?
[RUKO]
Rise and shine!
[yells]
[CHIYORI] W-Wait!
Who are you? What do you want?
Um, well, you see--
Want me to donate
to your religion?
Or join some pyramid scheme?
Too bad!
I don't have any money!
No, we just--
[CHIYORI gasps]
What?
We just want to
ask you if we can be friends.
If you wouldn't mind.
[CHIYORI]
Say what?!
This has gotta be
some kind of trick!
Right!
There's no way anyone
would wanna be friends
with someone like me!
You guys are just
trying to rob me!
[sobbing]
[HITOE]
Oh, no.
[ELDORA]
Well, at least you tried.
I feel bad.
This is never gonna work
if she doesn't trust us.
[ELDORA]
Ah, just give her time.
I'm sure she'll come around.
I bet she'll be all,
"Yeah, let's all be friends,
like you asked,
is that okay?"
Something dumb like that.
This is really embarrassing.
[ELDORA] Well, when
that finally happens,
just promise you'll treat
my partner good, 'kay?
Here goes!
See ya, card! Bye!
Wait! You can just climb
out of a card that way?
[ELDORA]
Yep!
Well, you girls
take care now, you hear?
--[ELDORA humming]
--[RUKO] Uh...
[RUKO]
Eldora...
She really did love Chiyori.
That was so sweet of her.
She's not the only nice LRIG.
Yuzuki's done so much for me.
I'm so grateful.
C'mon, stop.
And besides,
it's only natural isn't it?
We think of LRIGs
as tricking their Selectors,
but I realized something
when I became one.
LRIGs are like any
other girl in this game.
They get hurt, too.
And some of them make
the ultimate sacrifice
for their Selectors.
Midoriko.
Yeah, you're right.
All of the girls who are
involved in these Battles
get hurt.
We're all the same.
[IONA]
No.
[IONA] There is one girl who's
different from all the others.
That's Mayu.
She's jealous of
all the other girls.
And that's why she crushes
their wishes the way she does.
Ruko.
I need you to take me somewhere.
To Urith.
All right, here it is.
[URITH (I)]
Construction's almost done,
and this is going to be
my room, believe it or not.
You weren't here
for the fan event,
but I fought against Ruko
in this very building.
She was as beautiful
as she was powerful.
[chuckles]
You, on the other hand...
You're the exact
opposite of Ruko.
Pathetic.
Despite all of your tough talk,
you haven't been able
to kill anybody.
[AKIRA]
But wait...
That girl.
Don't you remember
what you said?
[URITH (I)] And it wasn't just
her wish, but her very life
that you snatched
away from her.
[gasps]
Please, that poor girl
was dying when you battled her.
--Some victory.
--[AKIRA] I don't care!
It never mattered to me whether
that girl was alive or dead.
Back then, a win was a win.
I was so different.
[AKIRA sobbing]
Why? This thing!
It's gonna make
my face so ugly!
[GIRL 210A]
What are you saying?
Now you look on the outside
just like you do on the inside.
You're the most disgusting
person in the whole world.
[AKIRA crying]
[GIRL 210A]
You're worried about your face
when your entire
soul is twisted.
[AKIRA screaming]
[AKIRA]
She was right.
Every single thing about me
was filthy and disgusting.
Yet, still,
you took your hands.
Instead of being repulsed,
you reached down
deep within my soul.
I truly thought you were
trying to save me then.
You like to
find things of beauty
and break them into
tiny pieces, don't you?
You take things
that are truly lovely
and make them
filthy and corrupt.
You used me to
get what you wanted.
I was simply a pawn.
Just a tool you used
to force Ruko to fight you.
My, how surprising.
And here I thought
you were a hopeless idiot.
Perhaps I should've given
you an inkling of credit.
So I suppose now you
wanna have your revenge?
Though the odds of you
doing so are laughable,
what do you hope to gain by
beating me in a Selector battle?
Do you want
to see me ruined,
like you did the last Iona?
Or just maybe...
You want to put a scar on me
that would mirror the
nasty one you're sporting?
[AKIRA]
I do.
But I'll heal it.
The scar that I'll give you...
It will be a pure
and beautiful wound
inflicted on you
by my boundless love.
But it's also that
same deep, abiding love
I have for you that's
gonna heal that scar in turn.
I'll become an LRIG.
And once I've turned back
into a human again,
the first thing that I'm
gonna do is track you down.
And then scar you.
Then I'll battle
again for my wish,
and guess what
that's gonna be?
To heal your scar.
Then I'll be
an LRIG again,
and then a human,
and an LRIG after that.
And then every single time,
from here on out,
I'm gonna leave
a scar on your body.
A physical reminder
of something.
Akira Aoi's love for Urith.
Like the last one I left!
And see, by doing this,
you won't be able to
simply pull my strings
and get rid
of me that easily!
I'm gonna leave a
permanent mark on you.
One that'll make sure
you'll never forget me!
[URITH (I)]
You're an interesting one.
I'll give you that.
All right.
Then let's get to it!
If you're battle-hungry,
then Tama and I are starving.
[TAMA]
Ru... I'm sorry.
You see...
During that last battle, when
those dark feelings came in
and took control of me,
I had a thought.
[TAMA] If that wish
could come true...
My wish...
I'd do anything
to make it happen.
Anything.
Even if I make people cry!
Here I come!
You piece of shit!
[STAFF A]
You wanna see Iona?
[RUKO] Yes, it's important
we speak with her right away.
Oh, hey, I remember you.
You're Iona and
Akira's friend, right?
How's Iona's wound?
Wait, what?
[STAFF B]
Hold on a second.
You mean you girls haven't
heard what happened to her?
[BOTH gasp]
[HITOE] A Battle put
Urith in the hospital?
That's odd.
Yeah, I know.
I wonder what really happened.
[YUZUKI] I'm getting
a bad vibe from this, guys.
I just hope that
Tama's okay and didn't get--
[gasps]
What's wrong, Yuzuki?
[YUZUKI] A Battlefield
just opened up somewhere!
[RUKO]
Huh?
Can we find out
who's battling?
Um, maybe.
Iona, can you tell us
what's going on?
It's strange,
but I can't sense much.
It's almost as if the battle
is being hidden by something.
Or by someone.
[RUKO gasps]
You think it's--
[screaming]
[panting]
[yelling]
Okay, Tama, now grow!
[BOTH gasp]
[TAMA]
Ru...
Stay away, I don't want
you to see me like this.
I'm begging you.
Please don't come here.
[KAZUKI] That shop sure had a
good selection of singles, huh?
[HANAYO (Y)]
Yeah.
[KAZUKI]
Yuzuki!
[car horn blares]
Wow, that was close.
Hey, let's go get
something to drink.
Something's wrong.
You've been
acting strange lately.
You know that, right?
So that explains it.
All those looks
you've been giving me.
Uh...
[HANAYO (Y)] Since when
have I been acting strange?
A week ago?
Two weeks ago?
Yuzuki...
Who's better,
the new me or the old me?
Please be honest.
I don't understand.
What do you mean?
Listen, I'm--
[gasps]
[IONA]
Yes, I believe it's this way.
Tama!
[HITOE]
Hey, wait, I just got a text!
You did? From who?
I don't recognize the sender.
"If you want to
meet Iona Urazoe..."
"Head here."
[gasps]
[RUKO]
Urith! Urith!
Urith.
Urith?
Where's Tama?
Let me talk to her!
Tama?
[IONA]
That email was very literal.
What?
This isn't Urith anymore.
It's the real Iona.
So you mean the first
one and not someone else
using her body, the way
Urith or an LRIG would?
[IONA (REAL)]
Lrig.
Been awhile, hasn't it, Lrig?
How strange.
We meet once again and
you look just like me now.
Huh? You just call her Lrig?
Yes, of course.
It's what I've
always called her.
[IONA]
LRIG.
[IONA (REAL)]
Lrig?
So that's your name, is it?
Not exactly, but I don't
have one, so that'll do for now.
You're such a strange girl.
[IONA]
So what's your fondest wish?
Fondest wish?
Let me see...
To be honest, I wish I
wasn't Iona Urazoe anymore.
You see, back then, everyone had
such high expectations of me.
I needed to not only live up
to the Urazoe name,
but also to my
responsibilities as a model.
I had little time for myself.
[IONA (REAL)] The closest thing
I had to a friend was Lrig.
She didn't say much
and I didn't ask much.
And amidst all the craziness,
I found playing WIXOSS
to be relaxing, even fun.
Lrig and I battled
alongside each other.
And then...
An Eternal Girl was born.
I went to the White Room,
met Mayu,
and found out
what had happened.
[MAYU]
Understand now?
You see what Selector
Battles are all about?
Are you upset?
Don't worry.
All you have to do
is become an LRIG
and drag a Selector
into Battle like I said.
[IONA (REAL)]
It doesn't matter.
My wish to no longer be
Iona Urazoe already came true.
So there's no reason
for me to battle anymore.
[MAYU]
Wait...
You don't care about
becoming a human again?
Your life is over.
Are you okay with that?
[IONA (REAL)]
Yes. It's fine.
[MAYU]
But that's wrong!
You're lying!
[IONA (REAL)]
What?
[MAYU]
That's not how it works!
Tell me this is terrible!
Tell me you want to become
a human again no matter what!
Let me hear you scream
and wail for it!
Or else it's completely wrong!
Absolutely wrong!
[IONA (REAL)]
And then, I became an LRIG.
Afterwards, I was an
LRIG for two other Selectors,
but knowing what I did, I
never coerced them into Battle.
Still...
They dreamt about
their wishes coming true.
So they battled anyway, right?
What's more, the Selectors
I was paired with
weren't suited for Battle.
They lost every single one
that they fought in.
As a result of that,
their wishes were reversed.
Sad.
Mayu didn't like me very much.
That's why she did what she did.
It makes sense.
Why else would she assign me
as an LRIG to weaker girls?
She'd do that?
Honestly,
I didn't care that much.
About myself, or even
about the other girls, but...
With all the tears I've seen,
this game became
really hard to bear.
And then I felt
something strange.
My real body...
This one, I mean...
It became so hollow.
[YUZUKI]
Hollow?
It was then I knew
what I had to do.
I needed to go back.
If no one resided
in Iona Urazoe's body,
then my life
would truly end.
[HITOE gasps]
I see now.
If Urith is no longer in
Iona's body, then that means--
[YUZUKI]
Her wish must have come true,
and an Eternal Girl was born!
This is complicated!
Yeah, like why the heck
is Iona's body hollow?
And if Urith became an LRIG,
then Tama should be a
human now, shouldn't she?
And in Iona's real body, too!
Yeah.
Right, Iona?
That's right, but Tama refused.
Wha--Refused?
Goodness, why didn't
you become Iona Urazoe?
No one would ever want to remain
as an LRIG, wouldn't you agree?
[TAMA]
I don't.
[MAYU]
Yes, you do.
I sensed your feelings.
You want to be human.
That way you can eat ice cream
with Ru under the summer sun
and buy scrunchies together.
Yes, but I'm originally a card.
I'm not a human.
If I were to become one,
that means I'd have
to take someone's body.
They'd become an LRIG, and that
could make them sad and lonely--
No more excuses!
I told you I could
sense your feelings!
So I know,
for that wish of yours,
you'd do anything!
Even if that meant you had to
make someone else miserable!
[TAMA] Urith unleashed
the bad version of me.
I don't want that me
to come out again.
[TAMA gasps]
But Ru...
I can sense her.
She's still looking
everywhere for me,
even after what
happened last time.
But...
Even though I wish
I could be with her,
Ru'll never
be able to find me.
Because the bad Tama
isn't the same Tama
that Ru knows and loves!
And that's why I
won't become a human,
because I can't let Ru find me,
even if it breaks my heart.
Ru and I were friends,
but we can't ever be again.
Besides...
I broke the promise
I made to her
so that her wish
could come true!
[RUKO] The thing is,
I have a wish to fight for!
It's to save you.
You and Tama!
[RUKO] Plus everyone else
who became LRIGs!
You'll see! I swear!
I'll bring you all
back to normal!
[TAMA]
That's Ru's wish.
I'm gonna do whatever it
takes to make it come true!
[IONA (REAL)]
Thanks for walking me here.
It's been a pleasure.
Be safe now.
You do the same.
[YUZUKI] This might be
weird coming from me,
but no more
Selector Battles, 'kay?
Never again, understand me?
Um... Anything to add, Iona?
Take care.
You know, I have to
give you credit, Lrig.
It seems you've grown up
a bit since last time.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry.
[YUZUKI]
Tama.
She's with Mayu now.
[YUZUKI] Just when we decide
to talk to Mayu, this happens.
That plan's shot.
No, not yet.
What?
I think the only thing
that's changed is the order.
Our plan was to get
her out of that room,
and then to convince her
to stop all these battles.
But now I just need
to win a few of them.
I'll become an LRIG and get
transported to the White Room.
To where Mayu and Tama are.
[gasps]
[RUKO] Once I'm there,
I'm sure I can get Mayu
to change her mind.
That's too dangerous,
Ruko, don't!
But we have to
get to her somehow.
[YUZUKI]
Are you nuts?
You can't face her alone!
[IONA]
Don't worry, she won't.
It's fine. I'll protect you.
Iona.
[RUKO]
Wait!
That's not right.
We've been calling
her "Iona" all this time,
but that was never even
her name in the first place!
Oh. Good point.
[IONA]
I'm fine with "Iona."
No way!
Let's come up with new name!
We can think
of something. Right?
Sure thing! What should it be?
[HITOE]
Uh...
Is there any word
that's your favorite?
[YUZUKI] Yeah, like how
Chiyori's was "Chorizo"
and she said she
wanted to be called that
when she became an LRIG.
What's yours?
Let me think.
[gasps]
[IONA]
It's snow.
[RUKO, HITOE gasp]
[IONA]
My favorite thing.
That's it. It's snow.
[IONA]
Back in that room with Mayu...
[MAYU]
Shut up!
[MAYU sobbing]
[MAYU]
Shut up. Shut up!
[IONA] We could never venture
into the outside world,
but we could still
hear it through our walls.
But sometimes it was silent.
[IONA]
The snow...
...took away all of those sounds
we didn't want to hear.
It was as if it
erased the entire world.
The snow was cold, yet kind.
Snow, huh?
What about "Yuki"?
[YUZUKI]
Yeah, "Yuki" means "snow"
and it's really pretty, too!
It is!
Wow, that's the
perfect name, Ruko!
"Yuki."
I like that. "Yuki."
[YUZUKI] Now we don't
have to say "LRIG Iona"
and "human Iona" or whatever.
Ah! Oh, darn, it totally
slipped my mind!
I meant to ask Iona about
who sent us that text
that told us
where to find her.
[RUKO]
Oh, right!
Ah, geez, that was
really stupid of us.
[IONA]
Is there an e-mail address?
[HITOE]
Oh, yeah.
Looks like their handle
is "Shadow Prince."
[RUKO] Do you guys know
anyone who goes by that name?
[gasps]
[YUZUKI]
Um, yeah. I do.
[MAYU]
Shiro.
You know what?
[MAYU]
Kuro is the bad girl.
And you're the good one.
Even so...
You're far more
spiteful than she is.
Spiteful? I am?
Let me show you.
You're like a beautiful rose.
[MAYU]
But one with thorns!
You cut me deeply!
And leave me alone
here to wither!
[gasps]
[MAYU] So now I've decided
to lock you away for good!
I'm such a fool!
Why did I let you go?
I never will again!
[TAMA]
No, please!
Ru!
[TAMA]
[HANAYO (Y)]
Welcome back, Kazuki.
You're so incredibly stupid.
Your wish is never
going to come true!
Now, let's begin.
[RUKO] Next time:
"That Locked Window."