- ( theme song playing )
- ( liquid bubbling )
- ( knife hitting board )
- WHA--?
OH.
OW!
I'VE GOT TO LEARN TO COOK
BETTER THAN THIS SOMEHOW.
OTHERWISE I'M GOING TO STARVE
WHILE I'M HERE IN TOKYO.
OH, YUCK.
I REALLY MISS ALL THAT STUFF
SASAMI COOKS.
( sighs )
- READY, HUH, RYO-OHKI?
HERE WE GO!
- MEOW!
MEOW.
- HEY, DON'T EAT
THE INGREDIENTS.
- MEOW.
- WE'RE HAVING SOUP
AND YUMMY KOBE BEEF
WITH NICE, FRESH CARROTS
ON THE SIDE.
- MEOW!
- FLIP IT WAY UP HIGH
TO COOK IT RIGHT.
WHEN THE STEAK IS FINISHED,
PUT IT ON THE PLATE.
THEN THE DELICIOUS
MISO SOUP IS NEXT.
TOO-DOO-DOO-TOO,
LA-LA-LA-LA,
BOOP-BAH-BAH-BOOP.
YAY!
( strikes gong )
THE SASAMI SPECIAL
IS READY TO EAT.
( giggles )
- I AM THE ABSOLUTE
NUMBER ONE,
THE CREATOR
AND THE RULER OF ALL.
THOSE OF YOU WHO HAVE
COMPLETELY FOLLOWED MY WILL,
COME FORWARD
AND BE BORN.
( chuckles )
WELL, HOW DO YOU DO,
MY DARLING
SERVANTS OF EVIL?
- ( birds chirping )
- ( footsteps )
- ( doorbell rings )
- ( exclaims )
YES, WHO IS IT?
- GOOD MORNING.
HI, TENCHI.
( laughs )
- ARGH!  SAKUYA!
IT'S SUNDAY MORNING.
WHAT IN THE WORLD ARE YOU
DOING HERE SO EARLY?
- DO I NEED A REASON
TO COME AND VISIT YOU?
- OH, NO, I DIDN'T
MEAN IT LIKE THAT.
- ( laughs ) TENCHI, I WANT
TO SHOW YOU AROUND TODAY.
WE'LL GO WALKING TOGETHER.
IT'LL BE LOTS OF FUN.
I MEAN, YOU JUST MOVED HERE AND
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN MUCH OF TOKYO,
SO I'LL BE YOUR TOUR GUIDE
IF YOU WANT.
- WELL, I'M NOT REALLY SURE.
YOU KNOW...
- SAY, TENCHI, YOU HAVEN'T
EATEN BREAKFAST YET, HAVE YOU?
- WELL, I WAS
GOING TO, BUT--
- GOOD, 'CAUSE I'M GONNA
MAKE BREAKFAST FOR YOU.
- YOU CAN GET ANYTHING
IN TOKYO, CAN'T YOU?
I MEAN, IT'S ALL
READY-MADE.
- YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT, TENCHI.
SHOPPING IS A FINE ART HERE.
YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE CAREFULLY.
I WENT TO FIVE
CONVENIENCE STORES,
AND YOU DON'T LIKE
MY BREAKFAST.
- NO, I LIKE IT,
REALLY.
- YOU DO?
NO KIDDING?
THEN GO AHEAD
AND DIG IN.
- RIGHT.  BON APPETIT.
- IS IT GOOD?
- OH, YEAH, IT'S GREAT.
- I KNEW YOU'D LIKE IT.
GO AHEAD AND HAVE SOME MORE.
- I'LL MAKE SOME TEA.
- THANKS.
- ( grunting )
- WHAT IS THAT CONNIVING GIRL
DOING IN TENCHI'S BEDROOM?
- HOW WOULD I KNOW?
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
SINCE IT'S SUNDAY,
I WAS PLANNING
TO VISIT HIM MYSELF, RYOKO.
- ( both growling )
- AYEKA, RYOKO,
BREAKFAST IS READY, YOU GUYS.
- I'M TOO BUSY
FOR THAT RIGHT NOW.
( both scream )
- ( Tenchi giggles )
- SHE'S ACTING LIKE A BRIDE
ON A HONEYMOON.
I ENVY--
I MEAN, DESPISE HER.
- OH, LOOK AT MY TENCHI.
LOOK AT THE WAY HE'S BLUSHING.
HEY, BACK OFF HIM, GIRL!
- THAT'S WHAT
I WAS GOING TO SAY,
BECAUSE LORD TENCHI IS MINE.
SHE CAN'T JUST GO
SNATCHING HIM AWAY
LIKE SOME HORRIBLE ALLEY CAT.
- YOU STAY AWAY FROM MY
TENCHI, I'M TELLING YOU.
- ( both grunting )
- Ryoko: HEY, LET GO OF ME.
- NO, I'M NOT LETTING YOU GO.
- I'M GONNA GET YOU BACK, AYEKA.
- I'M GONNA GET YOU.
OH, YOU, YOU--
- ( both scream )
- IS SOMEONE ELSE HERE?
- OH, NO, IT'S THE SOUND
OF MY NEIGHBOR'S TV.
I HEAR IT
ALL THE TIME.
YOU KNOW,
THEY PLAY IT SO LOUD
AND THE WALLS ARE
AWFULLY THIN.
- OH, THAT'S TOO BAD.
- ( giggles )
THOSE GIRLS WILL GET ME
INTO TROUBLE
IF I STAY HERE
ANY LONGER.
- GOOD MORNING.
OH.  HEY, WHAT ARE
YOU TWO DOING?
- WASHU?  GOOD.
YOU GOT HERE JUST IN TIME.
- YES, WASHU, CAN YOU
OPEN THIS PORTAL?
IT'S STUCK
OR SOMETHING.
- WE CAN ONLY REACH THROUGH
THIS FAR, SEE?
- WELL, IT'S A DIMENSION TUNNEL.
THERE'S NO WAY THROUGH.
UNLESS TENCHI OPENS IT
FROM THE OTHER SIDE,
WE CAN FORGET IT.
- OH, WELL, IN THAT CASE,
I'LL JUST BLOW IT OUT.
- WHAT?
NO, WAIT A SECOND,
RYOKO.
- Sasami: RYOKO, DON'T GET
CARRIED AWAY.
CALM DOWN.
- Ayeka: RYOKO, BE REASONABLE.
- FULL POWER.
( screams )
- ( Sasami screams )
- MEOW!
- ARGH.
- TOLD YOU
NOT TO DO THAT.
ALL YOUR POWER'S EXHAUSTED.
LOOK AT YOU.
- ( groans )
TENCHI.
- THEY'RE TRYING
TO FORCE THEIR WAY
THROUGH THE DIMENSIONAL
TUNNEL-- JUST WHAT I NEED.
- READY TO GO SEE
THE TOWN, TENCHI?
- HMM?  OH, YEAH.
- ( Sakuya giggles ) I'LL SHOW
YOU AROUND HARAJUKU FIRST.
- YEAH, SOUNDS GREAT.
- ( girls grunting )
- TAKE THIS.
TAKE THIS.  TAKE THIS.
- OH, IT'S NO USE.
WE'RE NEVER GOING TO
GET THROUGH IT THIS WAY.
- MEOW.
- WHOA.  HEY, THAT'S IT.
- MEOW?
- AHA!  MY, YOU'RE EXACTLY
WHAT WE NEED, RYO-OHKI.
- MEOW?
MEOW!
- Ryoko: QUIET.
WHEN YOU GET TO THE OTHER SIDE,
PULL BACK THE COMFORTER.
- MEOW!
- COME ON, YOU CAN GET
THROUGH THERE, YOU LITTLE RAT.
PUSH!
- MEOW!
- ( people chattering )
- COOL, HUH?
- YEAH, TERRIFIC.
- ( laughs ) LOOK AT THIS.
- MEOW!
- COME ON, RYO-OHKI,
QUIT HOLDING BACK.
YOU CAN GET
THROUGH THERE.
- YES, TRY HARDER.
GO ON.
- HEY, LEAVE RYO-OHKI ALONE.
YOU'RE HURTING HER.
CUT IT OUT,
YOU GUYS.
MISS WASHU,
MAKE THEM STOP.
- I TOLD THEM,
YOU CAN'T GET THROUGH THERE.
- LET'S GO THIS WAY.
- HMM?
- IT'S A LITTLE SHORTCUT.
COME ON, TENCHI.
- OH, RIGHT.
THIS IS KIND OF
A STRANGE AREA.
- IT'S-- IT'S GETTING
ALL FOGGY.
- WHOA.
LOOK OVER THAT WAY.
DO YOU SEE IT?
- WHAT AN EXTRAORDINARY
MANSION.
BUT I DON'T REMEMBER SEEING
ANYTHING LIKE THIS
AROUND HERE BEFORE.
HEY, MAYBE SOMEONE FAMOUS
LIVES HERE, YOU KNOW?
- WELL, WHOEVER LIVES HERE,
THEY MUST HAVE A TON OF MONEY.
I MEAN, THIS PLACE IS HUGE.
LOOK AT IT.
- HEY, TENCHI, WHY DON'T WE
TAKE A LOOK INSIDE?
- WHAT?  SAKUYA, NO.
WE'LL GET IN TROUBLE.
- ( Sakuya laughs )
- UH, HOLD ON A MINUTE.
- AHA.
OOH.
OH, WOW.
- SAKUYA, WE'RE NOT
ALLOWED IN HERE.
- ( both exclaim )
( both grunting )
- WELCOME TO THE HOUSE
OF THE ETERNAL PLEDGE.
- ( both gasp )
- MEOW.
MEOW.
- MEOW, MEOW.
- UH, WE'RE SORRY.
WE SHOULDN'T HAVE COME IN
WITHOUT ASKING.
BUT WE'RE LEAVING
RIGHT NOW.
- IT'S MY FAULT.
SORRY.
- YOU DON'T NEED
TO APOLOGIZE.  IT'S ALL RIGHT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I'M HAVING A PARTY TODAY.
SINCE YOU'RE HERE,
WHY DON'T YOU JOIN ME, PLEASE?
- WOW, A PARTY.
YEAH!
- HOW RUDE OF ME
NOT TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I AM HOTSUMA,
THE MASTER OF THIS ESTATE.
NOW PLEASE
COME THIS WAY.
- I THINK
WE SHOULD GO.
UH...
OH.
- THIS MANSION
IS SO BEAUTIFUL.
- IT IS PART
OF A LEGEND.
THE HOUSE
OF THE ETERNAL PLEDGE--
THAT'S WHAT
PEOPLE CALL IT.
LONG AGO A NOBLEMAN LIVED HERE
WITH HIS BEAUTIFUL DAUGHTER.
SHE FELL IN LOVE WITH A YOUNG
MAN WHO WAS ONLY A SERVANT.
BECAUSE THEY BELONGED
TO DIFFERENT CLASSES,
THE YOUNG LOVERS REALIZED THEY
WOULD NEVER BE ALLOWED TO MARRY,
SO THEY PLEDGED EVERLASTING LOVE
HERE, ON THIS SPOT.
THEN THEY ENDED THEIR LIVES
WITH THEIR OWN HAND.
- WHAT A SAD STORY.
- THEY SAY THE SPIRITS OF THOSE
LOVERS ARE STILL HERE.
THEY HELP
OTHER YOUNG LOVERS.
IF A COUPLE PLEDGES
THEIR LOVE IN THIS HOUSE,
THAT LOVE LASTS FOREVER,
EVEN BEYOND THE GRAVE.
- THAT'S ROMANTIC.
EVERLASTING LOVE?
- EXACTLY.  NOW YOU KNOW
WHY THIS PLACE IS CALLED
THE HOUSE
OF THE ETERNAL PLEDGE.
THIS LEGEND IS KNOWN
AROUND THE WORLD,
SO MANY YOUNG LOVERS COME
LOOKING FOR THIS MANSION.
BUT MOST BECOME
HOPELESSLY LOST.
THAT IS WHY IT IS ALSO KNOWN
AS THE HOUSE OF ILLUSION.
YOU ARE FORTUNATE
TO HAVE FOUND IT.
THAT MEANS YOU ARE DESTINED
TO BE TOGETHER.
- WHAT?
- NOW IT'S TIME TO PART.
WE'LL MEET AGAIN SHORTLY.
- ( exclaims )
- SAKUYA.  WHOA.
- TENCHI, HELP.
- I'M TRYING, SAKUYA.
- WHOA.
- ( chuckles )
- MEOW.
- RYO-OHKI.
- Ryoko: IF WE COULD JUST GET
THROUGH THE DIMENSION TUNNEL.
RYO-OHKI'S ALMOST THERE.
- Ayeka: THERE'S NO CHOICE.
- HUH?
- ( cackles )
- MEOW!
- YES!
- Ryoko: WE BROKE THROUGH.
NOW WE'VE GOT TO FIND TENCHI.
GO ON, RYO-OHKI.
WE'RE COUNTING ON YOU, BABE.
- THAT'S RIGHT, RYO-OHKI.
LEAD US TO LORD TENCHI.
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
- MEOW!
- THAT'S STRANGE,
RYOKO.
DID YOU NOTICE HOW QUIET
IT GOT ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- RYO-OHKI, HURRY.
WHERE HAS TENCHI GONE?
- ( sniffs )
MEOW.
- IT'S THAT WAY.
- HMM?
- WHOA, THIS FOG
IS SO STRANGE.
- TENCHI?
- WHA--?  HUH?
SAKUYA, YOU'RE DRESSED
LIKE A BRIDE.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- WELL, LOOK AT THE WAY
YOU'RE DRESSED, TENCHI.
- UH, MR. HOTSUMA,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WELL, THE PARTY
I TOLD YOU ABOUT
IS FOR YOUR WEDDING.
LOOK, YOUR LOVELY BRIDE
IS WAITING FOR YOU.
- AH!
- A WEDDING?  HOLD ON A MINUTE.
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU,
YOU WOULD NOT HAVE FOUND
THE HOUSE OF THE ETERNAL PLEDGE
IF YOU WERE NOT DESTINED
FOR EACH OTHER.
IF YOU SWEAR YOUR LOVE
TO EACH OTHER NOW,
IT WILL BE EVERLASTING.
YOU AND SAKUYA
WILL BE TOGETHER FOREVER,
EVEN BEYOND THE GRAVE.
- WHERE ARE WE?
I CAN FEEL THE EARTH SHIFTING.
- ALL I SEE IS FOG,
NO MATTER WHICH WAY I TURN.
AND IT'S GETTING
MUCH THICKER.
THERE'S AN EVIL PRESENCE OUT
THERE, AND I CAN FEEL IT, RYOKO.
- YOU'RE RIGHT, AYEKA,
AND I DON'T LIKE IT.
- MEOW, MEOW!
- AH, TENCHI'S
THAT WAY.
- NOW LET US BEGIN
THE MARRIAGE CEREMONY.
SINCE YOU'RE IN THE HOUSE
OF THE ETERNAL PLEDGE,
YOU NEED ONLY PLEDGE
YOUR DEVOTION TO EACH OTHER,
AND EVERLASTING LOVE
WILL BE YOURS.
YOU WILL BE TOGETHER FOREVER
AND EVER, YOUNG LOVERS.
- AH, TENCHI.
- YES, SAKUYA?
- Hotsuma: NOW TO BEGIN.
DO YOU, SAKUYA KUMASHIRO,
PLEDGE TO LOVE YOUR BRIDEGROOM
TENCHI MASAKI
TILL DEATH
DO YOU PART?
- I DO.
- AND NOW, DO YOU,
TENCHI MASAKI,
PLEDGE TO LOVE YOUR BRIDE
SAKUYA KUMASHIRO
TILL DEATH
DO YOU PART?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THIS ISN'T RIGHT.
SAKUYA AND I
BARELY KNOW EACH OTHER.
YOU BROUGHT US HERE
THROUGH SOME KIND OF MAGIC,
AND I WANT YOU
TO LET US GO.
- YOU MUST PLEDGE
ETERNAL LOVE TO SAKUYA.
- NO, I WON'T.
HUH?
( moans )
- DO AS I SAY
AND PLEDGE YOUR LOVE.
- I, TENCHI MASAKI,
PLEDGE THAT I WILL LOVE
MY BRIDE...
- MEOW, MEOW, MEOW!
- TENCHI IS INSIDE
THAT HOUSE?
- MEOW!
- RIGHT!
( grunts )
- WHY DID YOU SMASH YOUR FACE
INTO THAT DOOR?
- I CAN'T
GET THROUGH IT.
- IT'S LOCKED UP TIGHT,
BUT WE'VE GOT TO GET INSIDE.
- STEP ASIDE, AYEKA.
HIYAH!
- HUH?
- ( exclaims )
- Ryoko: TENCHI,
ARE YOU THERE?
- LORD TENCHI?
- MEOW?
- AH, YOU'RE HERE,
YOU GUYS.
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME.
THANK GOODNESS.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M SO GLAD I FOUND YOU.
ARGH!
- TENCHI, LOOK AT YOU.
WHY ARE YOU DRESSED LIKE THAT?
JUST WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OW!
TENCHI, YOU KNOW
YOU'VE GOT ME.
WHAT DO YOU NEED
THAT OTHER GIRL FOR?
SHE'S JUST
A LITTLE SCHEMER.
AND ANYWAY, SHE COULD
NEVER, EVER COMPARE TO ME.
YOU KNOW THAT.
- RYOKO, YOU'RE TWISTING
MY NECK.
- ( Sakuya exclaims )
- SAKUYA.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS,
MR. HOTSUMA?
- I TOLD YOU, THIS IS THE HOUSE
OF THE ETERNAL PLEDGE.
THOSE WHO DO NOT PLEDGE
ETERNAL LOVE
WILL RECEIVE
ETERNAL AGONY.
( laughing )
- TENCHI, HELP.
- RYOKO, MISS AYEKA,
PLEASE HELP ME.
WE'VE GOT TO SAVE SAKUYA
FROM HIM NOW.
- YOU'VE GOT
TO BE KIDDING.
WHY WOULD I SAVE THAT
SCHEMING LITTLE ALLEY CAT?
- WHAT SHE SAID.
- COME ON, TENCHI,
DON'T BOTHER WITH THAT GIRL.
HOW ABOUT SPENDING THE NIGHT
IN TOWN ALONE WITH RYOKO?
I'LL SHOW YOU SOME OF MY
SPECIAL POWERS.  IT'LL BE GREAT.
- LET HER GO!
- SHE'S MINE.
I'M TAKING SAKUYA WITH ME.
AND FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE
YOU WILL REGRET
THAT YOU DID NOT PLEDGE
ETERNAL LOVE TO HER.
- ( screams )
- OH, MY POOR TENCHI.
- ( moaning )
- PLEASE DON'T BE HURT.
- ( Sakuya exclaims )
- ( Hotsuma grunts )
- YOU DARE TO ATTACK
MY TENCHI?
YOU JUST MADE
A BIG MISTAKE, FELLA.
- WHOEVER YOU ARE,
I SIMPLY CANNOT ALLOW YOU
TO BRING ANY HARM
TO LORD TENCHI.
YOU HAVE NOW BEEN WARNED.
- MEOW!
- SILENCE!
- HANDS OFF TENCHI!
HA!  YOU GOT
WHAT YOU DESERVED.
- AH, TENCHI?
- WHA--?
- ( yells )
- ( both grunting )
- IT'S FANTASTIC.
WOW.
- WELL, YOU'VE GOT
SOME PRETTY GOOD MOVES.
- YOU'RE NOT BAD
EITHER.
- ( yells )
( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
WELL, WELL,
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- IT'S RYOKO.
AND WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
- HOTSUMA.
I LIKE YOU,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY I CAN'T STAY.
COME BACK AGAIN AND WE WILL
SETTLE THIS ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- HOTSUMA, HUH?
HMM.
- LORD TENCHI, I WAS SO WORRIED
HE MIGHT HAVE HURT YOU.
- MEOW.
- TENCHI, ARE YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, I'M FINE.
THANKS A LOT, RYOKO.
- THIS IS SO AMAZING.
THEY'RE REAL SORCERERS
AND THEY'RE YOUR FRIENDS?
AHH.
- MM...
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL INTRODUCE YOU.
YOU SEE, THEY'RE FROM
A SECRET GROUP CALLED
"THE MONSTER BUSTERS."
- WHA--?
- ( giggles )
- MONSTER BUSTERS?
- ( giggling )
- THAT'S SO SUPER.
OH, I SHOULD INTRODUCE
MYSELF TO YOU.
I AM SAKUYA KUMASHIRO.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING TO THE RESCUE.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
THANK YOU.  YOU MUST BE
THE NUMBER-ONE MONSTER BUSTER.
- AHH.
- AND YOU MUST BE
NUMBER TWO.
- HUH?
- HEY, CAN I HAVE
YOUR AUTOGRAPHS?
- ( girls giggle )
- MEOW.
- WHAT IS
WITH THIS GIRL?
- ( giggles )
- MEOW.
- TENCHI FINDS
THE WEIRD ONES.
- ( laughing )
- ( upbeat song playing )
- MEOW, MEOW.
MEOW.
- HELLO, IT'S ME--
YOUR DARLING LITTLE WASHU.
HUH?  YOU NEED
SOME MONEY
AND YOU WANT ME
TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT?
NO WAY.
THAT'S TOO MUCH TO ASK,
EVEN FROM AN AMAZINGLY
BRILLIANT SCIENTIST LIKE ME.
I CAN GIVE YOU SOME
TERRIFIC ADVICE THOUGH.
MAKE YOUR WAY TO TOKYO
AND FIND A PART-TIME JOB THERE.
WORK REALLY HARD, AND YOU CAN
EARN ALL THE MONEY YOU NEED.
HEY!  STOP MAKING FACES AT ME
AND GET GOING!
THE NEXT EPISODE OF THE NEW
"TENCHI MUYO" SERIES,
"MONEY!  MONEY!  MONEY!"