- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sakuya: TENCHI,
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
I HAD A WONDERFUL TIME TODAY.
I'VE COME TO REALIZE THAT...
EVEN THOUGH I STILL CAN'T
REMEMBER MY PAST,
IT DOESN'T MATTER ANYMORE,
BECAUSE I'M CREATING
NEW MAGICAL MEMORIES
EVERY TIME I'M WITH YOU.
AND I KNOW AS TIME GOES ON,
WE'LL HAVE MORE AND MORE
OF THEM TO SHARE.
WE'LL GO TO THE OCTOBER FEST,
AND GO ON
ALL THE RIDES TOGETHER.
AND ON CHRISTMAS,
WE'LL GIVE EACH OTHER PRESENTS.
OH, AND WE CAN VISIT THE SHINTO
SHRINE ON NEW YEAR'S DAY.
I THINK I WAS BORN TO FALL
IN LOVE WITH YOU, TENCHI.
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS
TO ME NOW, TENCHI.
EVERY DAY MY LOVE FOR YOU
IS BECOMING MORE
AND MORE REAL.
- ( meows )
- RYO-OHKI!
- Azaka: BE CAREFUL!
SHE'S A SORCERESS!
- WELL, I WARNED YOU.
I TOLD YOU THAT WHEN I PLAY,
I PLAY ROUGH.  HUH?
- ( murmurs )
- I WARN YOU, STAY AWAY!
THIS HOUSE IS TENCHI'S.
IT'S FOR TENCHI AND ME
TO SHARE OUR LIVES.
YOU CAN'T COME BETWEEN US,
MATORI!
I WON'T LET YOU GET
NEAR OUR HOME.
- OH.
WELL, LET'S SEE HOW CLOSE
I CAN GET.
YAH!
- ( grunts )
( gasps )
Ayeka: I WON'T DO IT.
I'LL NEVER GIVE IN.
OH, TENCHI.
- ( chuckles )
- ( screams )
- ( all gasp )
- AHH.
- Ayeka: OH, TENCHI.
( grunts )
- OH MY!  AYEKA!
- REALITY'S HARSH,
BUT THAT'S HOW IT IS.
- WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?!
( gasps )
- ( groans )
- ( meows )
( meows )
- RYO-OHKI, PLEASE TELL
TENCHI AND WASHU.
- Washu:
SASAMI'S BEEN KIDNAPPED,
AND AYEKA IS INJURED?
- ( meows )
- BUT WHY?
TENCHI'S THE ONE WHO
WILL SUCCEED ME
AS PLANET GUARDIAN.
WHY WOULD THEY KIDNAP
SASAMI AND NOT HIM?
- Tenchi: AYEKA, SASAMI...
- Yugi: SASAMI...
STAY HERE WITH ME.
I DON'T NEED ANYTHING ELSE.
PEOPLE, TOWNS,
THE OCEAN, THE SKY,
AND THE STARS.
I DON'T NEED ANY OF THEM
IF YOU ARE HERE.
COME ON.
LET'S MAKE THIS
A SPECIAL WORLD
JUST FOR YOU AND ME.
SASAMI?
- HUH?  WHAT IS THIS?
- YUGI IS ENTERING THE WORLD
FROM HER DIMENSION.
APPARENTLY, TIME HAS FROZEN
AS A RESULT
OF THAT PHENOMENON.
WE WOULD HAVE BEEN FROZEN
ALONG WITH EVERYTHING ELSE,
BUT THESE JEWELS ARE
PROTECTING US FROM HARM.
- YUGI.
( groans )
- TENCHI, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
YOU DON'T INTEND TO CONFRONT
YUGI BY YOURSELF, DO YOU?
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
SHE'S TOO POWERFUL, BELIEVE ME.
IF SHE CAN FREEZE TIME
ON A WHOLE PLANET,
IMAGINE WHAT SHE CAN DO
TO ONE ENEMY.
- STAND ASIDE, WASHU.
- I'M NOT MOVING.
- ( groans )
- HMM?
- UH?
- THIS IS NO TIME
TO LET YOUR ANGER
GET AWAY FROM YOU.
REMEMBER, YOU ARE A GUARDIAN
OF THIS PLANET.
YOU HAVE A VITAL
DUTY TO PERFORM.
- THE ONLY CHANCE WE HAVE
IS TO BRING
ALL THE GEMS TOGETHER.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'VE
GOT TO DO, TENCHI.
- SHE IS RIGHT, SON.
- ( growls )
LET ME GO!
- TENCHI!
- SORRY.
I KNOW YOU DON'T
WANT TO BE LOCKED UP,
BUT IT'S NECESSARY FOR NOW.
THIS ISN'T GOING
TO BE A PLEASANT SIGHT.
YOU SEE, SASAMI,
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO EVER CALLED ME "FRIEND."
WHO SMILED AT ME EVER.
THAT'S WHY I'M CHANGING
THIS WORLD FOR YOU!
I WANT IT TO BE
AN IDEAL PLACE
FOR US TO PLAY.
IT'LL BE PERFECT.
JUST FOR YOU AND ME.
AND I'LL SEE YOU
SMILE AGAIN.
SASAMI...
- ( panting )
IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF ME.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
HOW CAN I ASK THEM FOR HELP?
HOW CAN I EVEN FACE THEM?
I FELL FOR YUGI'S TRICKS.
I CAUSED THIS MESS.
AYEKA, RYOKO,
AND EVERYONE ELSE.
EVEN SASAMI.
THEY'RE ALL IN TROUBLE
BECAUSE OF ME.
I CAN'T ASK THEM
TO HELP ME NOW.
I-- I JUST CAN'T.
- Sakuya: TENCHI...
- ( panting )
YUGI!
- HAVE A BLAST.
IS THAT IT?
( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
- ( grunts )
- ( growls )
- YOU'RE MINE NOW,
LOVER BOY.
- ( growls )
- ( explosion )
- ( grunts )
- ( chuckles )
- HUH?
- FAREWELL.
- AAH.
( chuckles )
YOU GIRLS AREN'T TOO BAD,
I MUST SAY.
- ( both panting )
- ( grunts )
- OKAY.  I THINK I'VE HAD
ENOUGH OF THIS FOR NOW.
HERE!
- ( both scream )
- ( pants )
- SAKUYA, YES.
Tenchi: SHE WAS THERE,
RIGHT NEXT TO ME.
HER SMILE,
THE WAY HER EYES SPARKLED.
THAT WAS NO ILLUSION.
SHE'S NOT JUST A SHADOW.
SHE WAS REALLY THERE.
YUGI, YOU CAN'T
TAKE THAT AWAY FROM ME.
YOU CAN'T.  SHE'S REAL.
I JUST KNOW IT.
SHE HAS TO BE.
THIS IS ANOTHER ONE OF
YUGI'S SINISTER TRICKS.
- ( chuckles )
( laughs )
- YOU!
( shouts )
- ( panting )
- ( growls )
( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
TENCHI...
- ( laughs )
- ( Mihoshi and Kiyone shout )
- ( grunting )
- HERE HE COMES.
HE IS QUITE PERSISTENT.
Yugi:
LET HIM COME HERE, MATORI.
- HUH?
- IT'LL BE AN INTERESTING SHOW.
SIT BACK AND ENJOY IT.
- ( shouts )
- OHH.
( grunts )
- COULD YOU BELIEVE THAT GUY
IN THE CAFETERIA?
HE SPILLED EVERYTHING.
- I THINK
HE DID IT ON PURPOSE.
- HE LOOKED SO FUNNY.
- I KNOW.
- TALK ABOUT DESPERATE
FOR ATTENTION.
- AT LEAST HE WAS
HAVING FUN.
- SAKUYA.
- ( laughs )
- WAIT.
( murmurs )
- ( meows )
- ( clock ringing )
- SAKUYA, ARE YOU--?
- HMM?
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU SAW A GHOST.
- TELL ME--
I MEAN, SAKUYA...
- Yugi:
IS SOMETHING WRONG, TENCHI?
DON'T WORRY.
SINCE YOU CAME
TO MY CASTLE,
I THOUGHT I'D
ENTERTAIN YOU.
BUT IF YOU DON'T
LIKE THAT SHOW,
LET'S TRY ANOTHER SCENE.
- AAH.
- ( chuckles )
HOW COME YOU'RE LOOKING
SO SURPRISED, TENCHI?
SINCE THIS WORLD
IS MY CREATION,
I CAN DO ANYTHING
I WANT WITH IT.
AND MY SHADOW IS
UNDER MY CONTROL.
- ( growls )
YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS!
- TENCHI?  HI.
YOU LOOK UPSET.
ARE YOU OKAY?
- THERE.
I'LL JUST LEAVE YOU
HERE WITH HER.
DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
THIS WORLD IS
JUST FOR YOU TWO.
YOU CAN STAY HERE
WITH HER FOREVER,
OR ARE YOU WILLING
TO SACRIFICE YOUR DEAR SAKUYA
TO SAVE THIS PITIFUL PLANET?
( laughs )
- ( growls )
( grunts )
WHAT?!
- ( gasps )
( chuckles )
- ( grunts )
- YOU JUST DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU?
IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW UGLY YOU GET,
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO
TO CHANGE HOW I FEEL FOR TENCHI.
- ( shouts )
- LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
HOTSUMA,
THOUGH YOU WON'T UNDERSTAND.
- ( grunting )
- TENCHI'S HEART IS GENTLE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T CARE WHO HE'S WITH.
BECAUSE IT'S MY LOVE FOR HIM
THAT GIVES ME
THE STRENGTH TO TRIUMPH!
- ( Hotsuma shouts )
- DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE ALL WORN OUT.
A COUPLE OF TOUGH
SPACE BABES LIKE YOU?
- MIHOSHI, WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
RESORT TO EXTREME MEASURES.
- ( gasps )
YOU'RE NOT PUTTING THAT
IN YOUR BLASTER?
- JUST A SIMPLE
ANTI-MATTER EXPLOSIVE.
- IT'S EXPERIMENTAL.
YOU HAVE TO GET
PERMISSION FROM HEADQUARTERS
FOR THAT KIND OF THING.
- THERE'S NO TIME
TO WORRY ABOUT FORMALITIES.
HERE.
I'LL BE THE DECOY
AND DRAW HIS FIRE.
YOU'VE GOT TO
MAKE THE SHOT.
- KIYONE...
- HUH?
( gasps )
( chuckles )
CAN'T YOU DO BETTER THAN THAT?
COME ON NOW, GIRLS.
LET'S FINISH IT!
- AAH!
( breathing heavily )
- HUH?
- ( shudders )
- MIHOSHI.
YOU THREW YOURSELF
IN FRONT OF ME.
- KIYONE,
WATCH OUT.
OOH!
( grunts )
- ( laughing )
- ( gasps )
( grunts )
AH!  YOU'RE GONNA
PAY FOR THAT.
- ( gasps )
( panting )
( screams )
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, MIHOSHI.
WE CAN GO HOME NOW.
- THEN CAN WE EAT SOMETHING?
- ( music playing )
- THAT'S RIGHT, TENCHI.
JUST RELAX AND LEAVE
EVERYTHING TO ME.
PLAY YOUR PART,
AND YOU AND SAKUYA
CAN BE TOGETHER FOR ETERNITY.
IT LOOKS LIKE I'VE WON,
SASAMI.
- IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
- YEAH.
- I HOPE WE CAN
DO THIS AGAIN NEXT YEAR.
JUST THE TWO OF US.
- THAT'D BE NICE.
- NEXT YEAR, WHEN WE GO
TO SEE THE CHERRY BLOSSOMS,
I'LL MAKE A SPECIAL
LUNCH BASKET.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
( gasps )
- LISTEN TO ME.
YOU SAID THAT YOU LOVED ME
AND YOU WANT TO
BE TOGETHER.
BUT I HAVEN'T HAD
A CHANCE TO TELL YOU
THE WAY I FEEL YET.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO KEEP YOU GUESSING,
BUT I HAD TO REALLY
LISTEN TO MY HEART.
AND WELL,
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU TOO...
SAKUYA.
- TENCHI.
- HUH?
- Sakuya: I'M SO HAPPY.
I'VE WAITED SO LONG
FOR THIS MOMENT.
BUT I'M AFRAID
I HAVE TO GO AWAY NOW.
- SAKUYA?
- I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
OF COURSE...
IT'S SUCH A PITY.
BUT WE'VE HAD
A GREAT TIME.
TOO BAD WE CAN'T
JUST DREAM ON.
- WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO PULL ON ME?
I DON'T NEED YOU ANYMORE!
YOU'RE FINISHED!
- SAKUYA!
LET ME TELL YOU.
- NO.  YOU DON'T NEED
TO SAY ANYTHING.
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
NO MATTER HOW BEAUTIFUL
AND JOYFUL THIS MAY SEEM,
IT'S ONLY A DREAM WORLD.
AND PEOPLE CAN'T
LIVE ON ILLUSIONS.
TENCHI, YOU HAVE AN IMPORTANT
MISSION TO ACCOMPLISH.
PEOPLE ARE DEPENDING ON YOU,
AND YOUR HOME
IS WAITING FOR YOU.
THE TIME WE'VE
SPENT TOGETHER,
EVERY SMILE,
EVERY TOUCH,
ALL THE HOPES AND DREAMS
WE HAD FOR THE FUTURE,
I WILL CHERISH THEM ALL.
I WILL TREASURE
EVERY MEMORY.
AND MY TREASURE
WILL REMAIN RIGHT HERE.
I HAVE IT ALL NOW, TENCHI.
I WON'T WONDER
ABOUT MY PAST,
AND I WON'T FEEL LONELY
EVER AGAIN.
- GO AWAY!
- THEN I GUESS I MUST LEAVE.
- MM-HMM.
GOOD-BYE, TENCHI.
- ( sighs )
- ( gasps )
- OHH!
- AHH!
- ( gasps )
SASAMI?
( grunts )
( gasps )
- HUH?
- HEY.
- RYOKO?
I, UH...
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DID YOU FORGET
HOW TO TALK?
COME ON.
CHEER UP, TENCHI.
YO.
- AAH!
- DON'T WORRY.
I'M NOT HOLDING A GRUDGE,
YOU KNOW?
WE'RE STILL FRIENDS.
- RYOKO.
- ( grunts )
- WHOA!
- ( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
- AYEKA, WHAT IN THE WORLD?
- HI THERE.
I'M GLAD I MADE IT IN TIME.
- WE DIDN'T NEED YOUR HELP!
STAY AWAY FROM US.
YOU THINK I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO DO HERE?
SHOO, SHOO.
- YOU UNGRATEFUL BEAST, RYOKO!
YOU'RE AN EMBARRASSMENT
TO OUR ENTIRE GALAXY!
- WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY,
MISS PRISS?
- I SAID THAT
YOU'RE A DISGRACE!
- ( both growl )
Both: HUH?
- TIME TO GET RID
OF BOTH OF YOU.
HUH?!
- OH, POOH.
I THINK I HIT HER.
- THAT'S THE IDEA,
YOU TWIT.
- TENCHI!
- UH!
SA-- SASAMI?
- SASAMI!
- AYEKA.
- MIHOSHI, KIYONE?
- MIHOSHI, WERE YOU HURT?
- NUH-UH.
- YOU'RE HERE.
EVERYONE'S HERE.
HOW'D YOU FIND THIS PLACE?
- IT'S THE POWER
OF THE GEMS.
- WASHU?
- THAT'S RIGHT, TENCH.
THE GEMS LED US
TO THIS PLACE
BECAUSE WE ALL WANTED
TO COME BACK TO YOU.
- BUT I WAS WRONG.
I LET EVERYONE DOWN.
YOU SPLIT UP
BECAUSE OF ME.
- SASAMI.
SASAMI.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meows )
( meows )
- Ryoko: WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
A LOT, HAVEN'T WE, TENCHI?
AND NOW I KNOW WE'RE DESTINED TO
BE TOGETHER FOREVER, YOU AND I.
SO LET'S JUST DEAL WITH HER
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
WE'LL PAY HER BACK
A THOUSAND FOLD
FOR PLAYING WITH US
LIKE LITTLE TOYS.
GO, TENCHI, GO!
OHH!
I THINK I'M FALLING IN LOVE
WITH YOU ALL OVER AGAIN.
TENCHI,
MY TEMPERATURE IS UP
AT LEAST 10 DEGREES.
THE NEXT EPISODE
OF THE NEW TENCHI MUYO SERIES,
"PAYBACK."