- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( explosion )
- ( Ryoko laughs )
- ( minions laugh )
- ( hollers )
- ( rattles )
- ( gulps )
AH.
- ( explosion )
- ( laughs )
- ( cheering and laughing )
( laughter continues )
( sighs )
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH,
GOLD, JEWELS,
BEAUTIFUL DRESSES,
MORE SAKE THAN
I COULD EVER DRINK,
AND I FEEL EMPTY.
SOMETHING'S MISSING.
IT'S JUST NOT THE SAME
AS IT USED TO BE.
- AND NEXT
YOU'RE GOING TO TELL ME
THAT IT'S TRUE LOVE
YOU'RE MISSING OUT ON.
- HA! YOU DON'T KNOW
ME VERY WELL, DO YOU?
- HMM.
- WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
- I'M GOING OUT
FOR A WALK.
- OKAY, I'LL COME WITH YOU.
- LEAVE ME ALONE.
- GET OFF IT,
YOU SPOILED WENCH.
- News anchor: THESE MYSTERIOUS
GLOWING PHENOMENA
HAVE BEEN SIGHTED AT
THREE DIFFERENT LOCATIONS
AROUND THE TOKYO AREA.
OUR INFORMED
SOURCES TELL US
THEY MAY BE A RESULT
OF PLASMIC DISTURBANCE
WITHIN THE GEO-SPHERE.
- UH, THAT SURE IS STRANGE.
- SPECULATION ABOUT--
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, SAKUYA?
- HEY, I KNOW.
LET'S HAVE BREAKFAST.
I'VE BEEN LEARNING
TO COOK HERE.
YOU KNOW, I HAD TO,
LIVING ALONE.
- STAY WITH ME.
PLEASE DON'T GO.
DON'T LEAVE ME ALL ALONE.
- ( thinking )
SHE'S BEEN LIKE THIS
EVER SINCE SHE CAME OVER
YESTERDAY.
I WONDER WHY.
IT'S NOT LIKE HER AT ALL.
- AH, THIS IS AN ENDLESS BATTLE.
WE NEED A BETTER SYSTEM
FOR GUARDING THE HOUSE,
WHICH MEANS MORE TRAPS.
( strains )
- ( chopping )
- ( bubbling )
- YUGI...
- ( sizzling )
- WORK, WORK, WORK.
THERE'S NEVER ENOUGH TIME.
YOU NEED TO PAY MORE ATTENTION
TO WHAT YOU'RE DOING, SASAMI.
SASAMI.
WATCH YOUR FINGERS
WHILE YOU'RE CUTTING.
- OH.
- ( chopping resumes )
- ( computer beeps )
- THIS IS ASTONISHING.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THIS GEM HAD SO MUCH POTENTIAL?
TALK ABOUT A BIG SECRET, HUH?
AND THE NEXT STEP
OF MY RESEARCH
IS TO ANALYZE SAKUYA.
NOW, LET'S CHECK THE DATA.
AS THE GREATEST SCIENTIFIC
GENIUS IN THE UNIVERSE,
I'VE CREATED THIS DEVICE
TO DEMONSTRATE THE VALIDITY
OF MY HYPOTHESIS.
- I'LL CALL THIS
SECOND GENERATION
REPORT BOY TYPE
ANALYTICA.
THIS WILL REVEAL
ALL YOUR SECRETS, SAKUYA.
- ( beeping )
- ANALYSIS, ANALYSIS.
- HOTSUMA COULD HAVE PICKED
A BETTER PLACE FOR A HIDEOUT.
THIS PLANET'S NOTHING
BUT SNOW AND MORE SNOW.
WELL, I GUESS IT HELPS
KEEP OUR BASE FROM
BEING DISCOVERED
SINCE NO ONE WOULD EVER
WANT TO COME HERE.
( grunts )
TRUE LOVE, HUH?
( laughs )
HMM, YA'!
HERE'S ANOTHER ONE.  YA'!
( grunts )
HA! ( laughs )
WHEW, A GIANT SNOWMAN.
NOW, SASAMI
WOULD LOVE THAT.
AND I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT MIHOSHI WOULD DO.
I CAN PICTURE
THE WHOLE THING.
WHAA! SPACE POLICE
POLICEMAN, HELP!
THE SNOWMAN'S
TRYING TO EAT ME.
( giggles )
( laughs )
WHY AM I THINKING
ABOUT ALL OF THEM?
I'VE GOT TO GET
BACK TO THE BASE.
HOTSUMA FOUND THIS PLANET
AND SET UP OUR HIDEOUT.
I SHOULD SHOW MORE
APPRECIATION, I SUPPOSE.
IN FACT, HE'S DONE EVERYTHING
HE COULD DO FOR ME.
I'LL BE A LITTLE
NICER TO HIM.
( sneezes )
- ( clanging )
- ( shivers )
IT'S FREEZING IN HERE.
SOMEBODY OUGHT TO
TURN UP THE HEAT.
- Hotsuma: I THOUGHT I KNEW
WHAT I WAS GETTING INTO,
BUT I WASN'T READY
FOR THIS WITCH.
ALL SHE CARES ABOUT IS
MONEY, GETTING DRUNK,
AND WRECKING THINGS.
SHE'S A TOTAL ANIMAL.
WORSE, I THINK.
SHE STARTED
TO GROW ON ME,
BUT NOW ALL I SEE
IS A BARBARIAN.
I CAN HARDLY EVEN STAND
TO BE AROUND HER.
SHE DISGUSTS ME!
- HUH.
- SHE'S INSOLENT
AND I'M TIRED
OF DEALING WITH IT.
- ( gasps )
( grunts and growls )
( strains and growls )
( sighs )
HMM.
YOU'RE JUST LIKE
ALL THE OTHERS.
THEN AGAIN, I NEVER LIKED
YOU THAT MUCH, ANYWAY.
- WHO'S THERE?
WAS IT YOU, RYOKO?
- Yugi: SHE COULD
HAVE HEARD YOU.
( laughs ) WE'D BETTER
MOVE ON, DON'T YOU THINK?
- SHALL I ELIMINATE HER?  HMM?
- THAT WOULD BE WISE.
- ( chuckles )
- SAKUYA, I HAVE TO GO
TO MY PRACTICE SOON,
BUT I MADE US
A NICE BREAKFAST.
COME ON, CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S REALLY GOOD.
SAKUYA?
- WELL, I JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND THIS GIRL ANYMORE.
I GUESS, WE'LL JUST HAVE
TO TAKE HER OUT THEN.
TSUGARU, YOU CAN TAKE CARE
OF THE OTHERS, CAN'T YOU?
- OF COURSE.
- HMM.
- ( beeping )
DATA CAPTURE IN PROGRESS.
DATA CAPTURE COMPLETE.
( beeping )
- NICE GOING, ANALYTICA.
BRING THAT DATA
HOME TO MAMA.
WE'LL FIND OUT WHAT KIND
OF GAME SAKUYA'S PLAYING.
- ( sighs )
( sputters )
( sighs )
THIS FEELS SO PERFECT.
IT'S TRUE THAT ALL
I EVER WANTED
WAS TO WREAK HAVOC.
AND YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT ME
DRINKING TOO MUCH
AND BEING SELFISH,
BUT AT LEAST I'M UP-FRONT.
I DON'T SLINK AROUND
IN THE SHADOWS
AND SMEAR PEOPLE
AND STAB THEM IN THE BACK.
YOU LOWLIFE, AFTER
ALL WE'VE BEEN THROUGH!
( growls )
- AH, WHATEVER.
I JUST FEEL TERRIBLE.
OH, GEEZ, DO I LOOK
PATHETIC HERE OR WHAT?
HMM.
( echoes )
TENCHI.
SHOULD I GO BACK
TO OKAYAMA?
SO LONG, HOTSUMA.
GYAN, TRANSPORT BEAM.
- Minion:
YES, MA'AM.
- FAREWELL, RYOKO.
- ( gasps )
I FORGOT!
- ( explosions )
- SO MUCH FOR THE FAMOUS
PIRATE AND HER EGO.
- ( meows )
- Kiyone: WE'RE NOW PASSING
THROUGH SATURN'S ORBIT.
EARTH IS JUST
AROUND THE CORNER.
THE PLAN IS GOING
PERFECTLY...
EXCEPT FOR ONE THING.
HEY, HAVE YOU FOUND
THAT THING YET?
- NUH-UH, I'M STILL
LOOKING AROUND THOUGH.
UH?
OH.
- ( through P.A. )
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO EARTH
UNTIL YOU FIND IT,
UNDERSTAND?
- BUT THAT'S NOT FAIR.
UGH! OOH.
- ( through P.A. ) HOW'D YOU
LIKE IT IF I LEFT YOU
ORBITING THE EARTH IN NOTHING
BUT A SPACE SUIT, MIHOSHI?
HUH?
- WHAA!
I LOOKED EVERYWHERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE
IT COULD BE.
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
HOW COULD YOU LOSE THE GEM
TENCHI GAVE YOU?
YOU'RE SO SCATTERBRAINED.
( gasps )
YOU KNOW, IT SEEMS WE REALLY
BELONG TO EARTH SOMEHOW.
THAT'S NICE.
I FEEL LIKE
WE'RE GOING BACK HOME.
- ( cracking )
- ( grunting )
- ( chuckles )
NOW THAT'S TAKEN CARE OF.
AND THAT IS THE END
OF SAKUYA.
- SAKUYA.
I HOPE SHE'S OKAY.
I BETTER FINISH THIS QUICK
SO I CAN GET BACK
AND CHECK ON HER.
- HEY, TENCHI.
- HUH?
OH, UH,
HI, YOU, GUYS.
- YOU'RE ALWAYS WORKING.
DON'T YOU EVER
TAKE A BREAK?
IT'S SUMMER VACATION.
- HE CAN'T HELP IT.
HE'S GOT TO DO HIS TRAINING.
- WELL, WE'RE GOING
TO THE POOL.
WE'RE GONNA SWIM LAPS
AND COOL STUFF LIKE THAT.
( laughs ) DYING OF
JEALOUSY, AREN'T YOU?
- UH, YEAH RIGHT.
- NOW IF WE JUST HAD
SOME CUTE GIRLS
TO COME SWIMMING WITH US.
- MAYBE WE'LL MEET SOME.
AT LEAST WE'RE NOT
SWEEPING FLOORS LIKE TENCHI.
WITH ALL THAT TRAINING,
HE DOESN'T HAVE TIME
FOR A GIRLFRIEND.
THAT'S WHY
HE DOESN'T HAVE ONE.
- HUH?
- ( laughs )
- WELL, WE SHOULD
INTRODUCE HIM TO SOMEONE.
WE'LL SIMPLY SAY
THIS IS TENCHI.
HE'S NICE, BUT HE DOESN'T
KNOW ANY GIRLS.
- HUH? WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU KNOW I HAVE
A GIRLFRIEND.
- NOW DON'T MAKE UP STORIES,
TENCHI.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE JUST KIDDING.
UNLESS YOU'VE BEEN
HOLDING OUT ON US.
- THAT'S IT!
HE'S BEEN HIDING SOME GIRL.
WHO IS SHE, TENCHI?
COME ON, TELL US.
- ARE YOU LOSING YOUR MIND?
IT'S SAKUYA.
YOU KNOW, SAKUYA KUMASHIRO.
- Both: SAKUYA KUMASHIRO?
- WHERE'D YOU MEET HER?
WHAT DOES SHE LOOK LIKE?
- IS SHE CUTE?
- COME ON, BE SERIOUS.
YOU GUYS BOTH KNOW SAKUYA.
YOU KNOW, FROM OUR CLASS.
WE ALL WENT TO
THE BEACH TOGETHER.
- HMM.
- ALL RIGHT, IF THIS IS A JOKE,
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
JUST CUT IT OUT,
WILL YOU?
- WELL, OF COURSE I REMEMBER
THE BEACH AND EVERYTHING,
BUT AS FOR THE BABE,
'FRAID NOT.
- SAKUYA? YOU'RE PULLING
OUR LEG, AREN'T YOU?
WE'VE NEVER EVEN
HEARD OF HER.
- AH!
- Amagasaki:
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, BUDDY?
I THINK YOU MUST BE SUFFERING
FROM SUNSTROKE OR SOMETHING.
- Umanosuke: SAKUYA? WE'VE
NEVER EVEN HEARD OF HER.
- Tenchi: SAKUYA.
SAKUYA!
( running footsteps )
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
TENCHI!
WHAT GIVES?
- HE'S GETTING WEIRD.
- I HAVE A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS,
LIKE SAKUYA'S IN TROUBLE.
- ( birds twitter )
- COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON.
OWW!  OWW, OWW, OWW,
OWW, OWW, OWW.
- ( computer beeping )
- DATA INPUT COMPLETE.
NOW FOR THE NEXT PHASE...
( cracks knuckles )
MY NEW ORGANIC
FLUCTUATION FILTER
SHOULD REVEAL THE TRUTH
UNDERLYING THIS IMAGE.
JUST AS I THOUGHT.
SAKUYA KUMASHIRO
IS JUST A...
- ( footsteps )
SAKUYA!
( pants )
MAYBE SHE WENT
TO HER HOME.
BUT WHERE IS THAT?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW.
AH, HERE SHE IS.
YEAH, HER NAME'S RIGHT HERE
IN THE CLASS LIST.
THOSE GUYS WERE
JUST PUTTING ME ON.
EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
- ( Hotsuma chuckles )
THAT'LL TEACH HER.
THE END OF
THE FAMOUS SPACE PIRATE.
WE SHOULD HAVE GOTTEN
RID OF HER LONG AGO, YUGI,
WITHOUT COOKING UP
SUCH AN ELABORATE PLAN.
( chuckles )
- Ryoko: ALL PART
OF THE PLAN, HUH?
YOU TALKED ME INTO
COMING OUT HERE.
IT WAS BECAUSE OF TENCHI.
I CAN SEE THAT NOW.
YOU WANTED TO GET ME
AWAY FROM HIM,
BUT WHY?
THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING
TO FIND OUT!
HIYA!
( grunts )
- ( groans )
- ( wind rushes )
- ( grunts )
HOW DID YOU DO IT?
HOW COULD YOU GET
AWAY FROM THERE
WHEN I BLEW UP EVERYTHING?
- HMPH.
THIS IS WHAT SAVED ME.
I REALIZED THAT I'D LEFT
THIS PICTURE BEHIND.
SO I WENT BACK
TO GET IT.
- A PHOTOGRAPH?  RUBBISH!
- RUBBISH TO YOU MAYBE.
THIS IS MORE VALUABLE TO ME
THAN ALL THE GOLD
AND JEWELS WE PIRATED.
IT'S MY FEELINGS FOR TENCHI
THAT SAVED ME.
- TOO BAD HE DOESN'T FEEL
THE SAME WAY ABOUT YOU.
HE'S ALREADY GOT SOMEONE ELSE.
YOU KNOW THAT.
HE PLAYED YOU FOR A FOOL,
RYOKO, WORSE THAN I DID.
AT LEAST YOU KNEW
I WAS A PIRATE.
- NONE OF THAT
MATTERS TO ME.
NOT ANYMORE.
REWARDS?  THAT'S NOT
WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
I'M NOT LOOKING FOR ANYTHING.
ALL THAT MATTERS NOW
IS HOW I FEEL INSIDE.
- HOW DO YOU FEEL INSIDE, RYOKO?
- IT'S CALLED LOVE, HOTSUMA.
YOU KNOW? SOMETHING GUYS
LIKE YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
BUT IT'S SOMETHING
I CAN FEEL RIGHT HERE.
AND THAT'S ALL I NEED.
- ( gem rings )
- ( gasps )
- YOU'RE MINE.
- HUH?
- ( grunts )
- TENCHI!
HE'S IN DANGER.
- ( gem rings )
- AH! WHAT'S THIS?
- ( gasps )
HEY, IS THAT WHAT
I THINK IT IS?
IT IS!
BUT WHY IS IT GLOWING
LIKE THAT?
UNLESS SOMETHING'S WRONG.
- OH NO.
ALL SYSTEMS
INCREASE POWER!
WE'VE GOT TO GET TO EARTH FAST.
- ( engine roars )
- AYEKA, LOOK!
IT STARTED GLOWING.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
- ( gasps )
WHAT?  WHAT'S THAT LIGHT?
- ( birds chirp )
- HMM.
NOW COMES THE TEST.
- IT'S HERE ALREADY.
I THOUGHT WE'D HAVE MORE TIME.
WE'D BETTER MOVE
QUICKLY OR ELSE.
- ( grunts )
- ( groans )
- I'M OUT OF HERE.
- YOU'RE NOT GOING TO EARTH.
- TRY AND STOP ME.
- I'LL DO MORE THAN THAT!
- YOU'RE ALL TALK!
- AS SOON AS WE ENTER
EARTH'S ATMOSPHERE,
HEAD STRAIGHT
FOR OKAYAMA.
- ( explosion )
- ( metal clangs )
- ( buzzer sounds )
- WHAT HAPPENED
BACK THERE?
- WE'RE UNDER ATTACK.
PART OF THE WING BLEW UP.
THE SHIP
IS OUT OF CONTROL.
- BUT WHO'S ATTACKING US?
- HMM.
- ( beeping )
- HERE'S THE FILE I WANT.
A DIGITAL CAPTURE OF YUGI
DURING OUR LAST BATTLE.
AND IF I USE MY ORGANIC
FLUCTUATION FILTER...
IT ALL BECOMES CLEAR.
SAKUYA IS A PHANTASMAGORIC
EXTENSION OF YUGI.
SHE IS A CREATION OF YUGI,
BUT SHE DOESN'T REALLY EXIST.
SHE'S LIKE A SHADOW
LIVING IN A SHADOW WORLD.
- ( running footsteps )
( panting )
SO THIS IS
WHERE SHE LIVES.
( pants )
SAKUYA, IT'S ME, TENCHI.
ARE YOU IN THERE?
SAKUYA?
I'M COMING IN
SO GET READY.
HUH?
SAKUYA.
- ( crowd chatters )
- NO.
( sobs )
I DON'T WANT
TO BE ALONE.
TENCHI, I'M SCARED.
( echoes )
TENCHI!
- ( theme song plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meowing )
( meows )
- Tenchi: HELLO, SAKUYA?
IT'S ME.
NO, NOTHING
IN PARTICULAR.
IT'S JUST, WELL,
YOU'VE BEEN KIND OF DOWN LATELY.
AND I JUST THOUGHT MAYBE
IT'D CHEER YOU UP
IF WE WENT OUT SOMEWHERE,
YOU KNOW, TOGETHER
TO HAVE SOME FUN.
I MEAN, IF THAT'S
OKAY WITH YOU?
I DON'T MEAN TO INVADE
YOUR PRIVACY OR ANYTHING,
BUT, WELL, I JUST REALLY
WANT TO DO SOMETHING
TO MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF THE
NEW TENCHI MUYO SERIES...