- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ISN'T IT AMAZING? DID YOU
CHECK OUT THE HORS D'OEUVRES?
- WE'RE SURE WORKING A LOT.
- I WANT SOME HORS D'OEUVRES.
- IT WAS TWO YEARS AGO
ON THIS VERY DAY
OUR DELIGHTFUL DESTINY AND FATE
LED US HERE TO MEET LORD TENCHI.
YES, HE SHOWED GREAT GENEROSITY
BY TAKING ALL OF US STRANGERS
FROM OUTER SPACE HERE
INTO HIS OWN HOME.
TO SHOW OUR GRATITUDE,
WE DECIDED TO MAKE A HOLIDAY.
IT'S TENCHI ANNIVERSARY DAY.
AND THAT'S WHY WE'RE HAVING
THIS PARTY.
SO COME ON, EVERYONE.
LET'S CELEBRATE.
- ( laughs )
- GRAB A GLASS, EVERYBODY.
I WANT TO START THIS
WITH A VERY SPECIAL TOAST.
TO TENCHI,
WE LOVE YOU, TENCHI.
- RYOKO!
- ( gasping )
- ( laughs )
SORRY, TENCHI.
- ( laughs ) THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
- THIS IS IT.
TENCHI LIVES RIGHT NEAR HERE.
TENCHI.
( inaudible )
- I LOVE TENCHI.
I'LL ALWAYS LOVE HIM.
THAT'S WHY I HAVE TO
SEE HIM NOW.
I'LL FIND HIM
AND I'LL TELL HIM HOW I FEEL.
I JUST HAVE TO TELL HIM
ONE MORE TIME.
- I FEEL KIND OF SORRY
FOR HER.
I THINK I'LL GIVE HER
A LITTLE HELP.
- ( cackles )
- ( men and women laughing )
- COME ON, TENCHI.
OPEN YOUR MOUTH.
- I CAN FEED MYSELF, RYOKO.
- TENCHI, HERE.
I THINK YOU'LL FIND THESE
CUCUMBER ROLLS MUCH MORE SAVORY.
- MY SNACKS ARE MUCH BETTER,
TENCHI.  GO ON, TRY IT.
- SASAMI'S THE ONE WHO COOKED
ALL THIS FOOD.
NOW COME ON, YOU TWO.
GIMME A BREAK, WOULD YOU?!
- MMM!
- IT'S TRUE, SASAMI.
EVERYTHING YOU COOK IS REALLY
DELICIOUS,
BUT TODAY IT'S TASTIER
THAN EVER.
- THANKS, KIYONE.
I'M GLAD YOU LIKE IT.
I USED SOME SUPER FANCY COOKING
TRICKS TO MAKE IT SPECIAL
FOR TENCHI DAY.
- ( meows )
- EAT IT, TENCHI.  YOU CAN TAKE
IT RIGHT OUT OF MY MOUTH.
- IT'S REALLY NICE OF EVERYONE
TO THROW THIS PARTY FOR ME,
BUT I REALLY DIDN'T DO ANYTHING
TO DESERVE IT.
- HMM.
- IT WAS MY MOTHER'S NECKLACE
THAT CHANGED EVERYTHING.
- HE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW?  IF IT
WEREN'T FOR THOSE SPECIAL GEMS,
WE'D NEVER HAVE MET TENCHI
OR ANYTHING.
WE WOULDN'T KNOW EACH OTHER,
AND WE WOULDN'T BE HAVING
THIS PARTY TODAY.
- THAT'S TRUE, KIYONE.
- REMEMBER HOW BEATEN UP
WE WERE AFTER THE BATTLE?
- ARE YOU OKAY, AYEKA?
- ( snoring )
- ( groaning )
- IS SHE GOING TO BE
ALL RIGHT, WASHU?
- SHE'S VERY STRONG.
MUCH STRONGER THAN EARTHLINGS.
BUT SHE'S GRAVELY WOUNDED.
- OH, I SEE.  WELL...
- THANK YOU, TENCHI,
FOR COMING AND SAVING EVERYONE.
- IT WASN'T ME, REALLY.
- THE NECKLACE YOU'RE WEARING.
BE SURE THAT YOU
NEVER LOSE IT.
- HUH?
- IN TIME, I WANT
TO EXAMINE THOSE GEMS
AND LEARN ABOUT THEM.
I WANT TO UNDERSTAND
THEIR POWER AND YOURS.
- MISS WASHU.
WHO COULD HAVE IMAGINED
THERE WAS SUCH HORRIBLE POWER
IN THE NECKLACE
MY MOTHER LEFT ME?
- TENCHI.
- GRANDPA.  ( shouts )
TELL ME.
WHAT'S IN THESE GEMS?
- TENCHI, RIGHT NOW YOU MUST
THINK ABOUT THE GIRLS
WHO'VE COME HERE FROM SPACE.
FOCUS YOUR THOUGHTS
ON HEALING THEM.
AND BE AWARE THAT THERE WILL
COME A DAY, TENCHI,
A DAY WHEN YOU MUST LEARN
THE POWER OF THESE GEMS.
YOU'LL NEED THEM.
- GRANDPA.
- ( water sloshing )
- ( exhales ) HERE.
OW!
- ( gasps ) WOW!
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S JUST AS BEAUTIFUL HERE
AS ON PLANET JURAI.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT REALLY IS JUST AS LOVELY.
ALMOST.
IT IS OUR HOME PLANET.
- HEY, WHEN ARE WE GOING
BACK THERE, AYEKA?
YOU ARE THE PRINCESS
AND NOW THAT YOU'RE BETTER--
WELL, WHAT IS IT?
- I WANT TO STAY HERE.
- HUH?
AYEKA.
( gasps ) IT'S YOU, TENCHI.
- MISS AYEKA.
- LORD TENCHI.
THANKS TO YOU,
I'M COMPLETELY RECOVERED.
I'M ALL BETTER.
THANK YOU.
- MISS AYEKA,
YOU DON'T NEED TO BOW.
- HUH?
- UH, MISS AYEKA.
WHY DON'T YOU HAVE DINNER
WITH US?
I COOKED IT TODAY.
I MEAN, I TRIED.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S EDIBLE.
I'M NOT A REAL GREAT COOK,
BUT YOU'RE INVITED
IF YOU WANNA COME.
- I DO.
- AYEKA AND TENCHI.
AWW, THEY MAKE SUCH
A PERFECT COUPLE.
- I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT, MIHOSHI.
SHE'S A LUCKY GIRL.
- MM-HMM.
- ( snoring )
- Washu:
TENCHI, IS THAT YOU?
- HOW IS SHE DOING,
MISS WASHU?
- SHE HASN'T RECOVERED
CONSCIOUSNESS YET.
YOU KNOW, SHE DID GET HURT
AND RATHER BADLY.
- Man:
TENCHI, YOU HAVE A VISITOR.
- Tenchi:
SAKUYA.
- I KNEW IT, TENCHI.  SHE WAS
WANDERING AROUND THE BUS STOP,
TOTALLY LOST,
SO I OFFERED TO HELP,
AND SHE TOLD ME SHE
WAS YOUR CLASSMATE.
- HI, TENCHI.
THE REASON I CAME,
I WANTED TO TELL YOU
THAT I FEEL VERY--
- TENCHI, WE'RE RUNNING OUT
OF FOOD.
AYEKA, ATE IT ALL AND--
- ( screaming )
- YOU!  I THOUGHT WE GOT
AWAY FROM YOU.
WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- YOU'RE THOSE MONSTER BUSTERS,
BUT WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- THIS IS WHERE WE LIVE.
- YOU LIVE HERE IN THIS HOUSE?
IN TENCHI'S HOUSE?
- COME IN.
- ARE YOU HAVING SOME KIND
OF PARTY HERE?
- YES, WE ARE.
IT'S A VERY IMPORTANT PARTY
THAT WE CELEBRATE WITH TENCHI.
IT'S OFF-LIMITS
TO SCHEMING LITTLE
GATE CRASHERS.
- NOW HOLD ON, RYOKO.
THINK ABOUT IT.
IF SHE LEAVES NOW, SHE WON'T
UNDERSTAND THE SITUATION.
I THINK WE SHOULD MAKE OUR
LITTLE FRIEND HERE UNDERSTAND
ALL ABOUT THIS SPECIAL DAY
AND OUR SPECIAL
RELATIONSHIP WITH TENCHI.
- HOW'S THAT?
- IT WAS ON THIS DAY
TWO YEARS AGO
WE MET LORD TENCHI
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
IT WAS A SPECIAL DESTINY
OF THE HEART.
AND HE GAVE THESE
VERY RARE GEMS TO US ALL.
IT'S GONE.  MY GEM IS GONE!
- YOU MUST HAVE EATEN IT WITH
YOUR CUCUMBER ROLLS
OR SOMETHING.
GEE, WHAT A SHAME.
I'LL JUST SHOW HER MINE INSTEAD.
WHAT?  ( screaming )
IT'S GONE!
- GONE?
- ( clamoring )
- MINE'S GONE, TOO!
IT WAS A GIFT FROM MY MOTHER
AND NOW IT'S GONE.
HOW COULD IT HAVE
HAPPENED?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY'RE IRREPLACEABLE!
- ( cackles )
- ( meows )
- TENCHI'S NECKLACE!
- HIS MOTHER'S HEIRLOOM!
- THE GEMS ARE--
- GONE!
- IT WAS YOUR MOTHER'S HEIRLOOM?
- IT'S HER, TENCHI.
- HUH?
- SHE'S THE THIEF.
SHE DID IT!
- HUH?
- JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
THE GEMS WERE HERE
AND THEN POOF.
THEY WERE GONE.  ALL JUST
MOMENTS AFTER SHE GOT HERE.
WHO ELSE COULD
HAVE STOLEN THEM?  SHE DID IT.
- ME, BUT I--
- RYOKO!
- Ayeka: I MUST AGREE.
RYOKO HAS AN EXCELLENT POINT.
SHE MAY WELL BE RIGHT.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
- HMM?
- Tenchi: OH!
- I'M NOT.  I DIDN'T.
- LITTLE MISS INNOCENT.
THERE'S ONE WAY TO FIND OUT.
HERE!
- HMM.
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING HERE.
- HUH?
THEN SHE MUST BE HIDING
THEM SOMEWHERE.
COME ON, WHERE ARE THEY?
HEY, I ASKED YOU A QUESTION.
- I, I DIDN'T STEAL THEM.
- THAT'S A LIE.
- HOW COULD I?
I JUST GOT HERE.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
ABOUT THESE GEMS.
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
- ( screams )
- I NEVER LIKED YOU ANYWAY.
YOU'RE A SNEAK TRYING
TO STEAL TENCHI.
NOW WHAT DID YOU DO
WITH THOSE GEMS?
I KNOW YOU TOOK THEM.
- OW!
- HAND THEM OVER RIGHT NOW
OR ELSE!
- ( gasps ) MY HEAVENS.
- THE NEXT ONE'S GOING TO BE
FOR YOU
UNLESS YOU START TALKING,
YOU LITTLE THIEF.
- OH!
- TAKE THIS!
- STOP IT!
- LORD TENCHI!
- TENCHI.
- STOP THIS, RYOKO.
- GET OUT OF MY WAY.
I KNOW SHE STOLE THEM.
- SAKUYA WOULD NEVER
STEAL ANYTHING.
- ( whimpers )
OH, IS THAT RIGHT?  WHY ARE
YOU TRYING TO PROTECT HER?
GO TO HELL, TENCHI.
YOU FOOL!
- RYOKO!
- HOW COULD HE TAKE HER SIDE?
HOW COULD HE?
- RYOKO.
- HE STOOD UP FOR ME.
TENCHI.
- ALL RIGHT THEN,
WHO DID STEAL THOSE GEMS?
- Washu: I CAN ANSWER THAT EASY.
- MISS WASHU!
- WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN
AND WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN UP TO
ALL THIS TIME, WASHU?
- ( laughs )
TAKE A GUESS.
I WAS LOOKING FOR THIS.
- OH, WOW, WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S A GEM DETECTOR.
INVENTED BY A REAL GENIUS,
ME OF COURSE,
WASHU THE GREAT.
THIS BOX CAN DETECT A SPECIAL
ENERGY GENERATED BY THOSE GEMS.
LET'S TRY IT.
THE THIEF IS RIGHT
IN THIS ROOM.
- ( all gasp )
- THE THIEF IS...
THERE.
- ( screeching )
- ( laughs )
- ( all ) HUH?
- HE'S GOT THE GEMS.
- IT'S HIM.
- THAT LITTLE CREATURE.
WE SAW HIM HERE BEFORE.
- WHY, HE'S A ROBBER!
- ( screeching )
- HE'S GONNA HURT US.
- NO WAY. ( shouting )
EVERYONE, THOSE GEMS
ARE THE PROOF OF THE BOND
BETWEEN US AND TENCHI.  WE MUST
GET THEM BACK AT ALL COSTS.
- ( all ) YEAH!
- THE PROOF OF THE BOND?
OH, TENCHI.
- TENCHI.
THAT TIME LONG AGO, I COULDN'T
FORGIVE YOU THEN, EITHER.
OR RATHER, I WAS FRUSTRATED.
FRUSTRATED THAT I, RYOKO,
THE GREATEST SPACE PIRATE
OF ALL
SHOULD BE BEATEN IN BATTLE
BY A COUNTRY KID LIKE YOU.
I SWORE I WOULD DEFEAT YOU
AS SOON AS I RECOVERED
FROM MY INJURY.
BUT, TENCHI,
YOU WERE SO KIND TO ME.
- DAY BY DAY, YOU TOOK SUCH
TENDER CARE OF ME
EVEN THOUGH YOU YOURSELF
WERE WORN OUT.
NO ONE HAD EVER TREATED ME
LIKE THAT.
- ( sighs )
- ( door opens )
- ( gasps )
- I KNOW THAT YOU STILL
CAN'T HEAR ME,
BUT WASHU THINKS THAT
YOU'LL RECOVER SOON.
I HOPE SHE'S RIGHT, RYOKO.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU WAKE UP,
I WANNA SHOW YOU
AROUND THE EARTH.
- YOUR VOICE WAS SO KIND.
YOU TOLD ME STORIES
ABOUT AMUSEMENT PARKS
AND HOT SPRINGS AND ALL THE FUN
PLACES TO SEE ON PLANET EARTH.
YOU TOLD ME ABOUT THE DELICIOUS
FOOD WE WOULD EAT TOGETHER
AND SO MANY OTHER GOOD THINGS.
AND WHEN YOU FINISHED YOUR
STORIES, YOU WOULD LEAVE.
EXCEPT FOR THAT ONE NIGHT
WHEN THE MOON WAS FULL
AND YOU STAYED BY MY BEDSIDE
ALL NIGHT LONG.
I DON'T KNOW WHO THIS HAPPENED,
RYOKO.
I KNOW I COULD NEVER
MAKE IT UP TO YOU
I'M SO SORRY. I DIDN'T WANT
TO HURT YOU.  BELIEVE ME.
YOU HAVE A RIGHT TO WANT
REVENGE.
I WISH I COULD
MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
I SWEAR.
RYOKO, PLEASE.
OPEN YOUR EYES.
- EW.
- TENCHI.
- RYOKO!
- TENCHI, WHAT?
- THAT'S HIM UP THERE.  HE'S
THE ONE WHO STOLE THOSE GEMS.
- HUH?
- ( shouting )
- I SEE.  SO YOU'RE THE ONE,
YOU LITTLE WEASEL.
WHAT YOU'VE STOLEN IS MY BOND
WITH TENCHI.
I WILL NEVER FORGIVE YOU!
I'M GONNA BLOW YOU UP.
- ( screams )
- RYOKO.
OH, THANK GOODNESS.
I WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
YOU FINALLY WOKE UP.
- WHAT'S WITH THIS SORRY FACE
OF YOURS?
IS THAT THE FACE OF THE MAN
WHO DARED TO BLAST RYOKO,
THE GREATEST SPACE PIRATE
IN THE UNIVERSE?
- WELL, NOW HOLD ON.
- JUST TO MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
BLAST ME AGAIN, TENCHI,
I'M GOING TO KEEP THIS
LITTLE GEM.
- YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
GIVE IT HERE.
- BY THE WAY, MY FRIEND,
I'VE DECIDED TO USE YOUR PLACE
AS MY NEW HIDEOUT.
- NO, YOU'RE KIDDING.
- UNH-UNH.
YOU'RE STUCK WITH ME.
- ( clears throat )
- HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU ALL DOING HERE?
- AND HOW DID YOU GET
ALL THE GEMS BACK?
- IF YOU'RE GOING TO STAY HERE,
RYOKO,
THEN I'LL JUST HAVE TO
STAY HERE AS WELL.
IT'S PART OF MY DUTY
AS A PRINCESS AND GUARDIAN.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST ADMIT YOU
WANT TO LIVE HERE WITH TENCHI?
- MM-HMM.
- ( laughing )
- IT IS TRUE THAT KEEPING AN EYE
ON A SPACE PIRATE LIKE RYOKO
IS AN IMPORTANT DUTY
FOR THE POLICE FORCE.
- YOU'RE WORSE THAT AYEKA.
YOU JUST WANT TO STAY HERE,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
- ( growls )
- THIS PLANET IS RATHER
COMFORTABLE TO LIVE ON.
I WANT TO STUDY THE POWER
OF THESE GEMSTONES FURTHER.
SO I THINK THAT
I'LL STAY HERE AS WELL.
- I DON'T WANT ANY OF YOU
AROUND HERE.
GO BACK TO WHATEVER PLANET
YOU CAME FROM.
YOU'RE ALL A BUNCH OF SNOOPS.
- SNOOPS? I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW
THAT I'M THE FIRST PRINCESS
OF THE JURAI ROYAL FAMILY AND NO
ONE HAS EVER CALLED ME A SNOOP.
SO DON'T DO IT AGAIN.
- YEAH?
SNOOP, SNOOP, SNOOP,
SNOOPY SNOOP.
I'LL CALL YOU ANYTHING I WANT,
MISS PRISSY PRINCESS.
- ( growls )
- HEY, CUT IT OUT,
BOTH OF YOU.
YOU CAN LIVE HERE TOGETHER
AS FRIENDS.  WE ALL CAN, RIGHT?
- YOU REALLY MEAN IT?
- Tenchi:
HUH?  WELL, YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT!
- ( cheering )
- Tenchi: WHAT AM I GETTING
MYSELF INTO?
- NOW LET'S GET ON
WITH OUR TENCHI DAY PARTY.
COME ON, EVERYBODY.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- TENCHI.  UH--
- ( laughing )
- ( chattering )
- THERE'S NO PLACE FOR ME.
NOT HERE.
- Katsuhito: MISS.
- ( gasps )
- IT'S NOT SAFE
TO WALK ALONE AT NIGHT.
DID YOU FIND
WHAT YOU CAME FOR?
- NO, ACTUALLY,
I WAS SURPRISED.
I SURPRISED MYSELF BY COMING
ALL THE WAY HERE TO SEE TENCHI.
BUT NOW I SEE THAT
I DON'T BELONG.
- DON'T LEAVE NOW.
STAY HERE WITH US TONIGHT.
WE'LL FIND YOU A COMFORTABLE
PLACE TO SLEEP.
TOMORROW YOU CAN GO BACK
TO TOKYO WITH TENCHI.
YOU MAY SEE THINGS
DIFFERENTLY BY THEN.
- SO THEY ALL STICK TOGETHER.
I DON'T SEE HOW,
BUT IT'S VERY IMPRESSIVE.
WELL, ANYWAY,
AT LEAST NOW I KNOW.
( laughing )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meows )
- HI, I'M KIYONE.
I FINALLY DID IT, MIHOSHI.
I FOUND A PERFECT PART-TIME JOB
FOR US.
WE'RE GOING TO WORK
ON A NEW EXCAVATION SITE
OF ARCHAEOLOGICAL IMPORTANCE--
HUH?
OH, NO, ISN'T THAT AYEKA?
WHAT?
SHE'S COME TO FIND TENCHI.
I'VE GOT A FEELING SOMETHING BAD
IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
HEY, THAT'S NOT AZAKA
AND KAMIDAKE.
LOOKS LIKE I WAS RIGHT
ABOUT SOMETHING BAD HAPPENING.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF THE NEW
TENCHI MUYO SERIES--
"THE GUARDIANS OF OLD."