- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- TV Announcer: THE LONG,
SHINING TAILS DEVELOP
AS THEY ORBIT THE SUN.
THESE TWIN COMETS
ARE CALLED
THE MANUKETA COMETS.
THEY'RE NAMED AFTER MR.--
- Washu: WOW.
- Mihoshi: I WISH I
COULD RIDE ON ONE.
- Kiyone: WOULDN'T IT
BE AMAZING?
LOOK!
- HOW CAN YOU SIT AROUND
WATCHING TV
AT A CRUCIAL
TIME LIKE THIS?
- Mihoshi: AYEKA, CHILL OUT.
IT'S TIME WE DID
SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
WE MUST ACT NOW.
WE CANNOT SIMPLY
IGNORE IT!
- IGNORE WHAT?
- ARE YOU ALL BRAIN-DEAD?
I'M TALKING ABOUT TENCHI
AND HIS SUSPICIOUS
ROMANTIC RELATIONSHIP
WITH THAT AWFUL GIRL SAKUYA.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
WE HAD TO PUT OFF
OUR INVESTIGATION
UNTIL WE TOOK CARE OF
THAT STRANGE GIRL YUGI
WHO ATTACKED US?
WELL, NOW IT'S TIME
TO GET TO THE BOTTOM OF IT.
- HOW DO YOU PLAN TO CARRY OUT
THE INVESTIGATION?
- WE'LL ALL TRAVEL TO TOKYO
TO SEE TENCHI
AND GET THE STORY
DIRECTLY FROM HIM.
- THAT'S NO BIG DEAL.
WE'LL USE THE
DIMENSIONAL TUNNEL.
- I'M AFRAID
THE DIMENSION TUNNEL'S
STILL OUT OF ORDER.
AND IT'LL TAKE ME ALL DAY
TO FIX IT.
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME?!
NOW I'M UPSET!
HONORABLE FATHER
MESSED THIS UP.
SO WE'LL JUST BORROW
MONEY FROM HIM
TO TRAVEL TO TOKYO
BY BULLET TRAIN.
- Washu: SORRY.  HE SPLIT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY THAT, HUH?
- I FOUND HIS NOTE
THIS MORNING.
- Noboyuki:
"I'M GOING ON A TRIP.
PLEASE DON'T TRY AND
FIND ME. NOBOYUKI."
- HE RAN AWAY
AND LEFT US STRANDED HERE!
YOU BUILD US A FLYING MACHINE.
IT'LL ONLY TAKE YOU
THREE SECONDS.
- I CAN'T AFFORD
TO TAKE THE TIME
TO DO THAT
RIGHT NOW, ALL RIGHT?
I'VE GOT SOME
IMPORTANT RESEARCH.
I NEED TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT GEM POWER IS
BEFORE WE FACE
THAT GIRL AGAIN.
- WAIT, DON'T YOU
TAKE OFF TOO.
- IT'S TIME FOR US
TO GO OUT ON PATROL.
- DO WE HAVE TO?
- OF COURSE.
IT'S OUR DUTY.
WE'RE THE GALAXY POLICE.
NOW COME ON.
LET'S GET GOING.
- RIGHT NOW?
- SORRY, AYEKA, BUT DUTY CALLS.
- WAIT UP!
I'M BEING CALLED TOO.
- ( growling )
THAT JUST LEAVES US.
THERE'S NO CHOICE
BUT TO HAVE YOU ACCOMPANY ME.
RIGHT?
( gasps )
RYOKO, LET'S GO.
- I'M NOT GOING WITH YOU.
- WHY NOT?
- WELL, BECAUSE...
( silent )
- ( silent )
I DON'T NEED TO
CHECK UP ON HIM.
I TRUST HIM.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
RYOKO, HOW CAN YOU
DO THIS TO ME?
ALL RIGHT, FINE!
RUN OUT ON ME!
I'LL GET TO TOKYO MYSELF,
YOU'LL SEE!
THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M OFF TO BE WITH TENCHI.
( groans )
I JUST REMEMBERED
I DON'T EVEN HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY FOR
A CHEAP BUS TICKET.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
- Sasami:
ARE YOU OKAY, RYO-OHKI?
- ( meowing )
- HUH?
HEY, SASAMI.
- NO, RYO-OHKI
CAN'T TAKE YOU.
SHE'S NOT FEELING WELL!
- ( growls )
- OH, SORRY.
OH.
- TV Announcer:
WE'RE TALKING TO WORLD-TRAVELER
GANTETSU SARUMOTO.
IS IT TRUE YOU
LOST YOUR WALLET
ON YOUR LAST TRIP,
MR. SARUMOTO?
- I SURE DID, AND WITHOUT
IT, I DIDN'T HAVE
A CREDIT CARD
OR ANY MONEY.
- HMM? HUH?
- I MANAGED TO FINISH THE TRIP
BY HITCHHIKING
THE REST OF THE WAY.
I MET SUCH NICE PEOPLE
WHO GAVE ME RIDES.
I'M SO TOUCHED
BY THEIR KINDNESS.
( sniffs )
- HITCHHIKING!
THAT'S IT!
MY TRANSPORTATION SOLUTION!
- YAY! THIS IS THE LAST ROOM
WE HAVE TO CLEAN UP.
( gasps )
- WE'RE LEAVING NOW.
- BUT WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- TO SEE TENCHI.
- ( gasps )
- ( meows )
- WHY DON'T YOU AND I  FIND A
WAY TO HELP HER GET TO TOKYO?
- Tsugaru:
BUT WHY?
- TO SHOW HER
THE HAPPY COUPLE.
IT'LL SERVE MY PURPOSES
BETTER THAN
ANY OTHER CHEAP TRICKS
TO DESTROY THE BONDS OF TRUST
AMONG THE MASAKI FAMILY.
- DON'T TROUBLE YOURSELF
WITH THIS TASK.
YOU'RE STILL RECOVERING
FROM YOUR LAST BATTLE.
LET ME HANDLE IT.
I KNOW SOMETHING WE CAN USE
AND IT HAPPENS TO BE
HANGING AROUND RIGHT NOW.
I'LL PUT IT
TO WORK FOR US.
IT'LL BE FUN.
- HI!
- I DON'T LIKE DOING THIS.
THIS IS EMBARRASSING.
- ( honking )
- GET READY.
HERE COMES ANOTHER ONE.
HI, HELLO, THERE.
COULD YOU
GIVE US A RIDE?
- ( coughing )
- HI.
- ( tires screech )
- ( car doors open )
- HEY, WHAT'S A BABE LIKE YOU
DOING HITCHHIKING?
LOSE YOUR LITTLE FRIEND
AND COME PARTY WITH REAL MEN.
- YEAH, LET'S GO.
- Both: ( scream )
- NOW SCRAM!
- Both: OH, LET'S
GET OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW!
- HI.
- ( car stops )
- UH-OH.
- Both: SORRY, MY MISTAKE.
- HI.
- Seniors: ( chattering )
- BABY, YOU CAN WAIVE AT ME
ANY OLD TIME.
- SHE'D BE A PERFECT BRIDE
FOR MY GRANDSON.
- HI.
- WHY IS SHE WAIVING AT US?
- DON'T KNOW, BUT SHE'LL NEVER
GET A RIDE LIKE THAT.
- TRY HARDER!
WIGGLE YOUR THUMB
AND STICK YOUR LEG OUT TOO.
- ( laughs )
( thinking )
LITTLE BRATS.
- Sasami:
WE MIGHT AS WELL QUIT.
WE'D BETTER FACE IT.
WE'RE JUST NOT GONNA GET
FROM OKAYAMA TO TOKYO
BY HITCHHIKING.
- HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
- THE POWER OF
MY LOVE FOR TENCHI
WILL TAKE US ANYWHERE
WE WANT TO GO,
EVEN THE MOON. DON'T DOUBT
IT FOR A MINUTE, UNDERSTAND?
- ( motor runs )
- I'LL NEVER GIVE UP,
YOU HEAR ME?
NEVER!
- ( laughs )
- Masayo:
NEED A RIDE TO TOKYO?
- Both: HUH?
( gasps )
- WANT A RIDE?
- OH YES.
YES, BUT WILL YOU TAKE US
EVEN IF WE DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY?
- WELL, HOP ABOARD.
- ( speaks French )
- I DON'T EVEN SPEAK FRENCH.
- ( engine runs )
- HERE WE GO.
- GOOD.
( thinking ) IT WON'T BE
LONG NOW. I'M ON MY WAY.
JUST WAIT FOR ME,
TENCHI, PLEASE?
- GOOD, IT WORKED.
WAIT, I MADE TWO.
I WONDER WHERE
THE OTHER ONE WENT.
OH WELL.
- Joe:
HAHAHA, I'M JOE RIDER,
THE FASTEST THING
ON TWO WHEELS.
NOBODY BEATS ME
AND MY SUPER-CYCLE.
- ( Sasami screams )
- HUH?
WHAT WAS THAT?
- Ayeka and Sasami:
( screams )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY PASSED ME
LIKE THAT.
- I HOPE YOU'VE GOT INSURANCE
FOR THIS THING!
- IT'S FANTASTIC.
- THEY CALL ME
KEN THE SPEED DEMON
BECAUSE NOBODY MOVES
FASTER THAN ME.
( laughs )
- ( screams )
- WHOA!
- ( screaming )
- I'M COMING, TENCHI.
DON'T FALL IN LOVE
WITH THAT GIRL.
I'LL BE ARRIVING ON YOUR
DOORSTEP ANY MINUTE NOW.
- ( bells ring )
- Sakuya:
WOW, THAT'S GREAT.
- HUH?
- I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE
SUCH A GOOD ARTIST.
- THANKS, I ALWAYS LIKE
DRAWING THINGS.
I MUST GET THAT
FROM MY DAD.
- WHAT IS IT?
- I CAN'T SAY YET.
IT'S NOT FINISHED.
- I CAN WAIT.
- IT MIGHT BE A LONG WAIT.
( chuckles )
- ( giggles )
- ( laughs )
- PUT THE PEDDLE TO THE METAL!
LET US FLY!
I'M COMING, TENCHI.
- ( meows )
-  ( birds twitter )
- SASAMI, WHATEVER YOU'RE
COOKING SURE SMELLS GOOD.
HUH?
- SASAMI'S NOT HERE.
SHE WENT WITH AYEKA.
- I'M HUNGRY.
- WELL, DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I'M NOT COOKING FOR ANYONE
BUT MYSELF RIGHT NOW.
THE KITCHEN'S ALL YOURS.
I'M GOING TO EAT
IN MY ROOM.
( sighs )
I GUESS I'LL HAVE
TO COOK FOR MYSELF.
- ( sighs )
I THOUGHT I WAS DEAD.
- HERE YOU ARE
BEING SO KIND TO US
AND WE DON'T EVEN
KNOW YOUR NAME.
YOU ARE?
- MASAYO, MASAYO MANUKETA.
- MY NAME'S AYEKA
AND THIS IS
MY LITTLE SISTER...
- SASAMI'S THE NAME.
- WHY'RE YOU
GOING TO TOKYO?
- ( Ayeka cries )
I'M SO GLAD YOU ASKED.
I'M INVOLVED IN
A HEART-WRENCHING,
TEAR-JERKING,
LONG-DISTANCE LOVE STORY
THAT I'VE JUST BEEN DYING
TO TELL SOMEBODY ABOUT.
- HERE SHE GOES AGAIN.
- I GAVE MY HEART
TO THIS WONDERFUL BOY
AND HOPE TO
ONE DAY MARRY HIM.
HIS NAME IS TENCHI MASAKI.
HE LEFT HOME
TO STUDY IN TOKYO
IN ORDER TO BECOME A BRIDE-GROOM
FIT FOR A PRINCESS.
OH, IT IS SUCH A TRAGEDY.
I CAN HARDLY GET
THE WORDS OUT.
IN TOKYO, THERE WAS A WICKED
SERPENT-LIKE GIRL
WAITING TO CATCH HIM.
SAKUYA THE STALKER
MUDDLED HIS MIND
AND USED HER WITCHY POWERS
TO TAKE HIM AWAY FROM ME.
SHE TRICKED HIM AND NOW HE'S
COMPLETELY UNDER HER CONTROL.
I COULDN'T JUST SIT BY
AND DO NOTHING
WHILE HE WAS DESTROYED.
SO I LEFT HOME AND
STARTED HITCHHIKING
TO SAVE MY FUTURE HUSBAND.
- TO PUT IT SIMPLY,
SHE'S GONNA SEE FOR HERSELF
HOW HE TRULY FEELS ABOUT HER
BECAUSE SHE LOVES
HIM SO MUCH.
- IT'S ALWAYS BETTER TO KNOW
THAN TO BE IN THE DARK.
- GOSH, IT SEEMS TO ME
LIKE YOU'RE ALSO
IN LOVE WITH SOMEBODY.
- YEAH, HIS NAME IS ISAO,
ISAO KETAUCHI.
NO ONE CAN BEAT HIM.
HE'S SO FAST.
- OH, MISS MASAYO,
I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND YOU.
GIVING RIDES TO HITCHHIKERS
REALLY HELPS YOU PASS THE TIME,
BUT YOUR REAL OBJECTIVE
ON THE ROAD OF LIFE
IS TO CATCH UP WITH
THE MAN YOU TRULY LOVE.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
MASAYO NEVER SAID THAT.
OH NO!
THERE SHE GOES.
SHE'S OFF IN HER
FANTASY WORLD AGAIN.
- THE MAN YOU LOVE IS THE
FASTEST MAN IN THE UNIVERSE.
NO ONE ON THE ROAD
HAS COME CLOSE TO
MATCHING HIS SPEED.
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN
SO FAR OUT IN FRONT,
HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW THAT
YOU'RE RIGHT BEHIND HIM.
BUT YOU'VE NEVER GIVEN UP.
YOU'VE SPENT HOURS AND HOURS
UPGRADING YOUR CYCLE.
AND FINALLY YOU ACHIEVED
THE POWER TO MATCH HIS.
AND NOW YOU TRAVEL
AROUND THE WORLD
HOPING TO FIND HIM
SO YOU CAN BE SIDE BY SIDE
FOREVER.
- THAT IS ENOUGH!
- I'M VERY DEEPLY MOVED
BY YOUR STORY.
IT'S SO ROMANTIC, MASAYO.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
HOPE YOU'RE
NOT OFFENDED.
( whimpers )
- ( gasps )
- ( fluttering )
- THANK YOU.
YOU ARE THE FIRST
AND ONLY PERSON
TO EVER TRULY
UNDERSTAND ME.
- YES, WE ARE ALIKE.
- FRIENDS FOREVER.
- MASAYO.
- AYEKA.
- YOU'RE BONDING IN
THE SISTERHOOD
OF WOMEN IN LOVE.
WE BETTER TELL
EVERYBODY THE NEWS!
- ( chatter )
- I SAW HIM!
ISAO'S RACING AGAIN.
WELL, DID YOU
COMPETE WITH ISAO?
- YEAH, BUT I WAS
NO MATCH FOR HIM.
- ( rumbling )
- ( panting )
- ( muttering )
- THE MYSTERIOUS ISAO
HAS SURFACED LIKE A WHIRLWIND
FROM NOWHERE.
NO ONE HAS ANY IDEA
WHO HE IS.
- HE'S AWESOME.
THERE'S NOBODY LIKE HIM.
- ( rumbling )
- ( panting )
- SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
HE THE ONE
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR?
WHERE ARE YOU?
MASAYO? AYEKA?
- I HEARD HIM COMING
ALTHOUGH I NEVER...
GOT A GLIMPSE OF
ANYTHING BUT DUST.
- WHERE'S ISAO?
- HUH? WHAT?
WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- TELL ME!
- AAH.
LADY, I CAN'T BE SURE,
BUT HE'S PROBABLY STILL
CRUISING AROUND OUT THERE.
I MEAN, HE WAS DOING
FIVE LAPS TO MY ONE.
( sighs )
- MASAYO, WAIT.
- HEY, WHERE DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE GOING?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO TAKE
THE GIRLS WITH YOU.
- GOT TO FIND ISAO.
YOU ARE A KOMABITO.
DON'T EVER FORGET THAT.
I ORDER YOU TO TAKE
THE GIRLS TO TOKYO
JUST AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
GOT THAT?
- HM-HMM.
- Ayeka: MASAYO!
- REMEMBER YOUR
MISSION, MASAYO.
- HEY, MASAYO, DON'T
LEAVE WITHOUT US.
- I WISH I COULD.
- WHAT'S BOTHERING HER?
- ( meows )
- SOMETHING'S
COMING THIS WAY.
- ( rumbling )
- WHAT EVER IT IS,
IT'S NOISY.
- IT'S HIM.
- ( rumbling )
- ISAO!
- WHAT? HOW DO YOU KNOW
IT'S HIM?
ALL I SEE
IS A PILE OF DUST.
- I CAN ALWAYS RECOGNIZE HIM.
OUT OF SIGHT, BUT NEVER
OUT OF MY HEART, DEAREST ONE.
AH, COME ON.
BETTER GET YOU TO TOKYO.
- DON'T YOU WANT TO
CATCH UP WITH ISAO?
- IT'S OKAY.
- NOT REALLY. YOUR DEAREST
LOVE IS GETTING AWAY
FROM YOU AGAIN.  HOW COULD--
- I SAID IT'S OKAY!
FORGET IT.
I HAVE TO TAKE YOU TO TOKYO
AND I KNOW YOU'RE
IN A HURRY TO GET THERE.
- THAT'S TRUE. ALL THAT I'VE
BEEN ABLE TO THINK ABOUT
FOR THE PAST FEW DAYS
IS GETTING TO TOKYO
AND SEEING TENCHI.
- AYEKA.
- LUCKILY, HE'S NOT RUNNING
AROUND THE WORLD
SO IT SHOULDN'T BE
TOO HARD TO FIND HIM.
SO LET'S GO.
WE'LL FIND ISAO
WHILE THE TRAIL IS HOT.
- YOU MEAN IT?
- TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I'M STARTING TO GET COLD FEET
ABOUT GOING TO TOKYO.
YOU SEE,
I'M A LITTLE FRIGHTENED.
TENCHI MAY NOT EVEN FEEL
THE SAME WAY ABOUT ME.
AFTER ALL, HE MAY
REALLY BE IN LOVE
WITH THAT GIRL SAKUYA,
YOU KNOW.
I'M NOT SURE I HAVE THE COURAGE
TO SEE HIM NOW.
BUT I DON'T FEEL
SO ALONE ANYMORE
SINCE I FOUND OUT WE SHARE
A SIMILAR PROBLEM.
I KNOW YOU HAVE THE COURAGE
TO FIND THE ONE YOU LOVE.
AND I WANT TO HELP YOU
IN YOUR MISSION.
AT THE SAME TIME,
YOU'LL BE HELPING ME
GET UP THE COURAGE
TO GO AFTER MY TENCHI.
SO LET'S GO AFTER YOUR ISAO.
- YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
- ( engine runs )
- ( screams )
- LET'S GO!
- ISAO!
- ( screams )
- ( panting )
- ( rumbling )
- THAT'S ISAO.
- ( panting )
- Sasami:
I THOUGHT HE WAS A BIKER.
- RUNNING IS ALL HE HAS
EVER WANTED TO DO.
- LOOK, ISAO, MASAYO'S
RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- HE CAN'T HEAR YOU.
HE'S FOCUSED ON FUNNING.
- THERE'S ONE WAY
TO GET HIS ATTENTION.
GO FASTER THAN HIM.
GO!
- ( meows )
- ( screams )
- ( panting )
- WE DON'T SEEM TO BE GETTING
ANY CLOSER TO HIM.
WE NEED TO FIND A WAY
TO SPEED UP.
- PLEASE LET ME
GET OFF THIS THING.
- HOW CAN YOU THINK
OF DESERTING MASAYO
WHEN SHE NEEDS US THE MOST?!
I'VE GOT IT.
THE BIKE WILL BE LIGHTER
AND GO MUCH FASTER WITHOUT US.
SASAMI, RYO-OHKI, OFF!
- OH, GREAT.  YES.
LET'S GET OFF.
LET'S GET OFF NOW!
BUT HOW?
WE'RE MOVING TOO FAST.
- GET READY, MASAYO.
- GOT YOU.
- ( panting )
( grunts )
- ( grunts )
- OKAY, JUMP.
- OH!
- ( all scream )
- COMING UP BEHIND YOU, ISAO.
- ( panting )
- ISAO!
HEY, ISAO!
IT'S ME, HEYYY!
- ( panting )
( gasps )
MASAYO!
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
- ( meows )
- THANKS, RYO-OHKI.
WONDER WHAT HAPPENED
TO MASAYO.
- Ayeka: MASAYO!
- THANK YOU SO MUCH,
AYEKA AND SASAMI.
NOW ISAO AND I
CAN GO BACK TO OUR COMETS.
- COMETS?
- I WISH THAT YOU BOTH
HAVE A VERY HAPPY LIFE.
- GOOD-BYE NOW.
DON'T GIVE UP, AYEKA.
- I PROMISE I WON'T.
GOOD-BYE, DEAR FRIEND.
I'M GOING TO FIND OUT
HOW TENCHI REALLY
FEELS ABOUT ME.
THANK YOU FOR GIVING ME
THE INSPIRATION.
- SO THOSE COMETS WERE LOVERS,
NOT TWINS, HUH.
I THOUGHT I WAS MAKING BIKERS
OUT OF BOTH OF THEM.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW THAT KOMABITO
TURNED OUT TO BE
A CROSS-COUNTRY RUNNER.
- ( sighs )
BUT WHERE ARE WE?
- APPARENTLY,
WE'RE IN SENDAI.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"IN SENDAI"?!
WHERE IN THE WORLD IS THAT?!
I WANT TO KNOW WHICH
WAY TO GO TO TOKYO!
- WE PASSED TOKYO A WAYS BACK.
WE WERE GOING SO FAST,
WE MISSED IT.
- ( meows )
- I'M NOT LETTING
THIS LITTLE MIS-CALCULATION
STOP ME.
I'M TELLING YOU
I'LL GET TO TOKYO
EVEN IF I HAVE
TO HITCHHIKE THERE
ALL THE WAY FROM AMERICA.
COME ON, SASAMI, LET'S GO.
TOKYO OR BUST!
- THAT'S ENOUGH WORK
FOR TONIGHT.
- ( doorbell rings )
- HUH?
WHO'S THAT?
NO ONE VISITS THIS LATE.
( gasps )
- ( groans )
- Tenchi: AYEKA?!
- AND SASAMI TOO!
GOSH, WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
YOU BOTH LOOK AWFUL.
- ( sighs )
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
( sighs )
- ( slurps )
- ( banging )
- GOLLY, SURE TOOK
THEM LONG ENOUGH.
- ( light breathing )
- WHAT COULD THEY
HAVE DONE IN TOKYO
THAT WIPED THEM OUT
LIKE THAT?
- ( giggle )
- YEESH, SHE'S OUT
LIKE A LIGHT.
MAKE SURE YOU TELL ME
IN THE MORNING
EXACTLY WHAT YOU DID.
NIGHTY-NIGHT FOR NOW.
( yawns )
- MASAYO, MAY YOU
ALWAYS BE HAPPY.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meowing )
( meows )
- Tenchi: I'M TENCHI MASAKI.
SAKUYA AND HER FRIENDS
ARE SETTING UP
A CREPE STAND FOR
THE SCHOOL FESTIVAL
AND I'M HERE TO HELP.
SOMEHOW THESE GIRLS
ARE ACTING STRANGE THOUGH,
LIKE THEY HAVE SOME KIND OF
SECRET PLAN OR SOMETHING.
AND THAT'S NOT ALL.
AMAGASAKI'S BEHAVIOR
IS EVEN WEIRDER THAN USUAL
THESE DAYS.
I WONDER WHAT'S GOING
ON WITH HIM.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF THE NEW
"TENCHI MUYO" SERIES
"LOVE MATCH."