- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meowing )
( screeching )
- TENCHI!
TENCHI, TENCHI!
COME BACK HOME, TENCHI!
TENCHI!
COME BACK!
- Girl: I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE GOING HOME TODAY.
IS ANYTHING WRONG
AT HOME, TENCHI?
- WELL, NO, I MEAN,
THAT IS NOTHING SERIOUS.
- HEY, I KNOW.
WHAT IF I GO BACK WITH YOU?
- WHAT?
- I WANNA SEE WHERE YOU GREW UP.
AND I'D LIKE TO MEET
YOUR MOTHER AND FATHER.
I'D BET THEY'D BE SURPRISED
IF YOU CAME HOME
WITH A FRIEND LIKE ME, HUH?
- SURPRISED?  YEAH, RIGHT.
THAT WON'T WORK OUT.
- WELL, IT WOULD BE KIND
OF SHORT NOTICE.
MAYBE I CAN MEET THEM
ANOTHER TIME, HUH?
- YEAH.  ( laughs )
- HERE.  TAKE THIS.
YOU CAN EAT IT ON THE TRAIN.
I MADE IT MYSELF
JUST FOR YOUR TRIP.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- NOW YOU HAVE A GREAT TRIP,
TENCHI.
- YEAH, THAT'S IT.
MAKE IT NICE AND PRETTY, AYEKA.
- IT JUST NEEDS
ANOTHER FLOWER.  OW!
- AYEKA!
- ( laughing )
- WOW!
THAT'S QUITE A SCAM.
- THIS IS OUR PART-TIME JOB.
- YEAH, BUT IT'S SO MUCH
MORE FUN WHEN WE DON'T HAVE TO
DO IT FOR MONEY.
- YES, THAT'S TRUE.
- WHEN WE DO IT FOR MONEY,
WE HAVE TO MAKE ZILLIONS
OF THESE FLOWERS.
- WHOOPS, SORRY.
- ( screaming )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP THERE?
YOU ALMOST HIT US.
- SORRY.  I'M TRYING
TO FIX THIS THING.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE DIMENSION
TUNNEL'S GONNA BE OUT
OF COMMISSION
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- THIS IS KIND OF WEIRD.
WHAT IS IT, MISS WASHU?
- DON'T TOUCH THAT.  WAIT!
- ( screaming )
- KIYONE, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- DOES IT LOOK LIKE
I'M ALL RIGHT?
- NOW DON'T GET ANGRY.
THIS IS A SPECIAL DAY.
WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE CELEBRATING, REMEMBER?
( laughs )
- HUH?
OH.  THAT'S RIGHT.
IT IS A SPECIAL DAY.
THE DAY WE GOT THESE.
- I REMEMBER.
- IT SEEMS LIKE IT WAS
ALL SO VERY, VERY LONG AGO.
TENCHI'S ANNIVERSARY.
WHOOPS!
I CAN PICTURE IT ALL PERFECTLY.
THE SKY WAS EXACTLY LIKE THIS
ON THAT DAY.
IF AYEKA HADN'T CHASED ME
TO THE EARTH,
I WOULD NEVER
HAVE MET TENCHI.
- OUR BLASTER MADE A DIRECT HIT
ON THEIR PROTECTIVE SHIELD.
- THE SHIELD'S REFLECTION
RATIO IS 88%.
OUR BLASTS HAVE
NOT PENETRATED.
- JUST KEEP SHOOTING.
WE'VE GOT TO GET THROUGH.
RYOKO, THAT SPACE PIRATE.
SHE HAD THE NERVE
TO STEAL THE JURAI LIGHTSTONE.
- AYEKA, HEY,
LISTEN TO WHAT I'M SAYING.
DON'T YOU THINK THAT WE
SHOULD LET THE GALAXY POLICE
HANDLE THIS STUFF?
- SASAMI, ARE YOU CRAZY?
THE LIGHTSTONE IS ONE OF
THE MOST CHERISHED TREASURES
OF OUR JURAI ROYAL FAMILY.
AND THE GALAXY POLICE
ARE INCOMPETENT BUNGLERS
WHO TRIED TO CATCH
RYOKO A THOUSAND TIMES
AND SHE ALWAYS MAKES
THEM LOOK LIKE COMPLETE IDIOTS.
- UH, EXCUSE ME.
WE CAN HEAR EVERYTHING
YOU'RE SAYING ABOUT US.
- YOUR HIGHNESS, PRINCESS AYEKA,
THE CHIEF OF POLICE
HAS ASKED THAT YOU WOULD PLEASE
LEAVE THIS MATTER TO US.
- IDENTIFY YOURSELVES.
I'M GALAXY POLICE
DETECTIVE FIRST CLASS KIYONE.
- MIHOSHI, AT YOUR SERVICE.
- DON'T LET ME STOP YOU.
YOU TWO JUST GO RIGHT AHEAD
AND YOU TRY TO CATCH RYOKO.
- both: YES, MA'AM.
- YEAH, WE DID IT.
- HMM?
- IF WE ARREST THAT
SPACE PIRATE RYOKO,
WE'LL GET A BIG RAISE
AND A PROMOTION.
NOT TO MENTION
WE'LL GET OUR POSITIONS BACK
AT HEADQUARTERS.
THIS IS OUR BIG CHANCE, PARTNER.
MIHOSHI, TRY NOT
TO BE YOUR USUAL
AIRHEAD SELF TODAY, PLEASE.
- YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
ATTENTION OUT THERE,
THIS IS THE GALAXY POLICE.
SEE THAT BIG RED STATION THINGY,
STOP AND PULL OVER!
WHAT IS THAT?
- IT'S A GIGANTIC LASER CANNON!
- TAKE EVASIVE ACTION!
- ( screaming )
- RYO OHKI!
- HOW DARE YOU,
YOU SPACE PIRATE.
I'LL SHOW YOU THE TRUE POWER
OF MY NEW EXTREME
BATTLE STATION, RYOKO.
- AZAKA, KAMIDAKE,
FIRE ALL TORPEDOES.
- YES, MA'AM.
- NOW HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT?
- HUH?  WHAT?
- ( Washu laughing )
GIVE IT UP, LITTLE GIRL.
I, WASHU, THE GENIUS MASTERMIND
CREATED THAT SHIELD
SO YOU'LL NEVER BREAK
THROUGH IT!
HMM.  HOW EXTRAORDINARY.
I'VE NEVER SEEN CRYSTALLIZED
ENERGY IN THIS SHAPE BEFORE.
SO THIS IS THE FAMOUS
POWER OF JURAI.
I SIMPLY CAN'T WAIT TO EXAMINE
ITS MOLECULAR STRUCTURE.
IT IS SO COOL!
( shouts )
- DOWN, GIRL.  YOU'RE NOT DOING
ANY OF YOUR WEIRD EXPERIMENTS
ON THAT ROCK.  THAT STONE IS
WORTH SO MUCH MONEY,
THAT WE'LL NEVER RUN OUT
OF CASH EVEN IF WE LIVE
FOR A ZILLION YEARS,
AND I'VE GOT BIG PLANS FOR IT.
- YEAH, SO DO I.
YOU PROMISED ME
A STATE OF THE ART
PARTICLE CONVERTER, REMEMBER?
AND I FULLY EXPECT YOU
TO PAY UP.
FOR A PIRATE LIKE YOU TO HIRE
A GENIUS LIKE ME,
IT'S GONNA COST SOME BUCKS
AND I DON'T MEAN CHUMP CHANGE.
- OKAY.  UGH!
SHE IS PERSISTENT
THAT JURAI PRINCESS.
I'LL GIVE HER THAT.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- OH, GOSH, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF FUEL.
THAT'S A PROBLEM.
- WHAT?
MY PROTECTIVE SHIELD
IS OUTSTANDING,
BUT I MUST ADMIT IT DOES TEND
TO USE UP FUEL RATHER QUICKLY.
- YOU BUILT IT OUT
OF SPARE PARTS, DIDN'T YOU?
- THE SHIELD IS GONE.  REACTIVE
ENGINE POWER IS DECREASING.
WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
YOU CAN QUOTE ME ON THAT.
- THAT'S JUST GREAT.
YOU CAUSED THIS.  YOU FIX IT.
- THERE'S NOTHING TO FIX.
WE'RE JUST OUT OF FUEL.
ERGO, WE NEED FUEL,
BUT THERE'S NO FUEL STATIONS
IN THIS REMOTE REGION
OF THE UNIVERSE.
BINGO.  WE CAN DRAW ENERGY
FROM THIS SOLAR SYSTEM.
THE THIRD PLANET HAS A MASSIVE
SUPPLY.  IT'S CALLED EARTH.
- ( screaming )
- THEIR PROTECTIVE SHIELD
IS GONE.
NOW'S THE TIME
FOR A FULL FRONTAL ATTACK.
- ABSOLUTELY.
THAT SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
- REACTIVE ENGINES ONE AND TWO
HAVE GONE OUT.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO MAKE
A RUN FOR THE EARTH QUICK.
WASHU, HANG ON GOOD AND TIGHT.
- THEY'RE GETTING AWAY!
- BUT WE'LL CATCH 'EM.
- SHIFT TO FULL POWER.
- YES, MA'AM.
- HUH?  THERE IT IS,
PLANET EARTH.
- MM-HMM.
- IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE HEADING
FOR THE EARTH.
- KIYONE, THE REAR MONITOR.
LOOK!
- OH, WHAT IS THAT?
PRINCESS AYEKA,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I THOUGHT YOU TOLD US
TO HANDLE THIS.
- WELL, YES, WITH MY HELP
OF COURSE.
I PLAN TO USE
MY THUNDERFLASH CANNON.
THAT'LL IMMOBILIZE THEIR SHIP.
YOU CAN RETRIEVE THE LIGHTSTONE.
- YES, MA'AM.
- LOCK ON THE TARGET.
- REMEMBER, THEY HAVE
THE JURAI LIGHTSTONE.
SO DON'T BLOW UP THEIR SHIP
NO MATTER WHAT.
- YES, WE UNDERSTAND,
YOUR HIGHNESS.
- WE'LL JUST RESTRAIN ITS OUTPUT
ENOUGH TO DISABLE IT.
- THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
THAT PRINCESS GIRL
IS GONNA FIRE HER THUNDERFLASH.
I JUST KNOW IT.
- NO, SHE'S NOT
'CAUSE I WON'T LET HER.
- THUNDERFLASH, UNLEASH!
- ( screaming )
- PRINCESS!
- WE'VE HAD IT, WASHU.
WE'RE FINISHED.  WE'RE THROUGH!
- NO, WE'RE NOT.  IT SEEMS WE'RE
BEING DRAWN DOWNWARD
BY SOME UNKNOWN POWER SOURCE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- THE PIRATE SHIP HAS ENTERED
INTO THE EARTH'S ATMOSPHERE.
- THEY'RE NOT GETTING AWAY
FROM ME.
LOCK ON AND FOLLOW THEM IN.
- YES, MA'AM.
- AYEKA.
- OH, THIS IS GREAT.
I'M LATE FOR MY EVENING CHORES.
GRANDPA'S GOING TO BE REALLY MAD
AND WHEN HE GETS MAD--
OH!  HMM?
WHAT'S ALL THIS?
- I LOCATED THE HIGH ENERGY
SOURCE THAT'S THERE.
- HUH?
- ( meows )
- WHY?
WHY CAN'T I COMMUNICATE
MY FEELINGS TO TENCHI?
( speaks Japanese )
YES, OH, THAT'S IT.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, AYEKA?
- HMM.  HE'S LATE.
LORD TENCHI IS VERY LATE.
HE SHOULD HAVE BEEN HERE
A LONG TIME AGO.
THERE'S NO EXCUSE.
OH, NO, MAYBE HE'S BEEN
IN AN ACCIDENT OR SOMETHING.
YOU WORRY WAY TOO MUCH,
AYEKA.
HE'LL SHOW UP SOON
JUST LIKE HE DID THE FIRST TIME.
DO YOU REMEMBER HOW
IT ALL HAPPENED?
- HUH?
AH, YES, I REMEMBER IT ALL
AS CLEAR AS CAN BE.
- THERE ARE NO SIGNS
OF LIFE DETECTED IN THE SHIP.
THEY MUST HAVE ABANDONED
THE CRAFT AND RUN AWAY.
VERY COWARDLY.
- OH.  THEY COULDN'T HAVE GONE
VERY FAR YET, RIGHT?
WE'LL FIND THEM, YOU'LL SEE.
- RIGHT.
- ( panting )
RUNNING CHASE ON A WEIRD PLANET
LIKE THIS WASN'T PART
OF OUR DEAL.
HOW DID I GET ROPED INTO THIS?
THAT'S WHAT I WANNA KNOW.
- NO ONE'S FORCING YOU.
STAY BACK AND GET CAUGHT
BY THE GALAXY POLICE
IF YOU WANT.
- YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING.
NOBODY'S GONNA PUT
A GENIUS SCIENTIST LIKE ME
IN SOME JAIL.
IT'S PREPOSTEROUS.
AND I'M NOT JUST THINKING
OF MYSELF, EITHER.
IT'D BE A GREAT LOSS
FOR THE SCIENTIFIC DEVELOPMENT
OF THE WHOLE UNIVERSE
AND YOU'D BE ON YOUR OWN!
- ALL RIGHT,
DON'T GET SO WORKED UP.
I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THIS WHOLE THING.
WE FIND OUR TARGET.
NEXT WE CAPTURE HIM
AND TAKE THE ENERGY FROM HIM.
THEN WE REPAIR THE SHIP AND GET
THE HECK OFF THIS PLANET.
THEY'LL NEVER KNOW
WHAT HIT 'EM.
- SOUNDS GOOD, BUT WHY DO I
DETECT SUCH A HIGH ENERGY
REACTION FROM OUR TARGET HUMAN?
HE JUST LOOKS LIKE
A PLAIN OLD ORDINARY LIFE FORM.
HMM?  OH!
- DARN.
- SHE DOESN'T KNOW WHEN
TO GIVE UP.
- SEARCHING, SEARCHING.
SEARCHING.
- SEARCHING. SEARCHING.
I DETECT LIVING ORGANISMS.
- I KNOW YOU'RE
OUT THERE, RYOKO.  HUH?
- THINGS SEEM TO BE GETTING
OUT OF HAND, RYO-OHKI.
- ( meows )
- OH, WOW, IT LOOKS KIND OF LIKE
PLANET JURAI HERE.
- ( screaming )
- THAT WAS A FATAL MISTAKE,
PRINCESS.
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE HAD TO DIE
IF YOU HADN'T BEEN SO FOOLHARDY.
UGH!  WAS THAT SUPPOSED
TO BE SOME KIND OF ATTACK
OR SOMETHING?
- ( growls )
- I AM AYEKA, THE FIRST
PRINCESS OF JURAI
AND DON'T EVER UNDERESTIMATE
MY POWER.
NOW COME ON, RYOKO,
YOU SPACE PIRATE,
YOU RETURN THE JURAI LIGHTSTONE,
AND I MAY EVEN LET YOU ESCAPE
- WITH YOUR LIFE.
- HA!  YOU THINK I'D GIVE IT
TO YOU JUST BECAUSE YOU SAY SO?
THAT'S A LAUGH.
LET'S SEE YOU TAKE IT.
( laughs )
- ( shouts )
- WELL, GO ON.
YOU'RE SUCH A TOUGH PRINCESS
COME AND GET IT.
- NO, WAIT, PRINCESS AYEKA,
PLEASE.
- LET US TAKE CARE OF HER.
- ( laughs )
YOU GUARDIANS ARE GOING DOWN.
( grunts )
NOT BAD.
- OUR TURN!
- ( screams )
- RYOKO!
- ( chuckles )
- ( grunts )
- YOUR INSULTS CAN NEVER
BE FORGIVEN.
BUT SINCE WE'RE IN THE PRESENCE
OF A PRINCESS,
WE WON'T PUNISH YOU IF YOU
RETURN THE JURAI LIGHTSTONE NOW.
- YOUR TIME IS UP.  SURRENDER
THE JURAI LIGHTSTONE AT ONCE.
- WHATEVER WAS I THINKING.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU ROYAL GUARDS
WERE SO TOUGH,
SO LET'S SEE
HOW YOU TAKE ...THIS!
- THERE IS NO USE TRYING
THAT MANEUVER AGAIN.
- SHE'S DISAPPEARED.
- WHERE IS SHE?
- YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO DODGE MY BLAST NOW.
NOT AT THIS DISTANCE.
SO LONG.  HA!
WHAT?  ( screaming )
- AZAKA, KAMIDAKE,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YES, THANK YOU, PRINCESS.
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR HELP.
- HANG ON, RYOKO.
- THEY GOT ME THIS TIME.
- SO THIS IS THE ILLUSTRIOUS
SPACE PIRATE RYOKO.
WELL, SINCE YOUR POWERS
ARE NO MATCH FOR MINE,
YOU MIGHT AS WELL GIVE IT UP
AND SURRENDER THE LIGHTSTONE.
- I'LL NEVER SURRENDER
AND IF YOU TRY TO FORCE ME TO,
I'LL--
- WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
- STAY CALM
DON'T GET CRAZY, RYOKO.
- I'LL BLOW YOU SKY HIGH
WITH THE JURAI POWER SEALED
IN THIS STONE.
- OH, NO!
- ( grunting )
- ( gasps )
- WHERE ARE YOU?
AYEKA, AZAKA, KAMIDAKE!
WHERE IN THE WORLD ARE THEY?
THEY JUST VANISHED.
AYEKA, AZAKA, KAMIDAKE!
( whimpering )
- ( screeches )
- ( shouts )
- ( gasps )
A HUMANOID ON THIS PLANET?
- A LITTLE GIRL?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
WHAT'S WRONG, LITTLE GIRL?
WHERE ARE YOU FROM
AND WHY AREN'T YOU
WITH YOUR PARENTS?
- I GOT LOST, YOU SEE?
- SOMETHING HUGE FELL
FROM THE SKY
AND CRASHED INTO THAT MOUNTAIN.
IT COULD CAUSE A FIRE OUT HERE.
IT'S DANGEROUS TO STAY HERE.
COME ON.
- WAIT!
- HEY!
- AYEKA, I'M COMING.
- HEY, COME BACK.
- ( groaning )
AZAKA, KAMIDAKE!
- WOW!  SO THAT'S THE JURAI
POWER THAT WAS HIDDEN
IN THAT LITTLE CRYSTAL.
- ( gasps )
- ( screaming )
- WHAT A SLUGGER.
- AYEKA, IT'S ME!
AYEKA!  AYEKA!
- SASAMI, NO, STAY AWAY.
- ( growls )
- AYEKA!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- WHO ARE YOU?
- WHAT IS THAT DEMON THING?
- YOU'RE IN DANGER HERE.
FLEE QUICKLY.
- WHOA!
- THIS IS--
IT'S MY MOTHER'S.
- THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE POWER SOURCE
WE WERE LOOKING FOR.  THE ENERGY
THAT DREW US DOWN HERE.
- HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
WHAT IS IT?
- ( screaming )
- NO!  ( panting )
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
- RYOKO.
- PRINCESS AYEKA,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( sirens wailing )
- HMM.
- IT'S SURE GOOD TO BE HOME.
- Girl: TENCHI'S HOME!
LORD TENCHI!
- Ryoko: SO HE'S HOME, HUH?
- YES, HE'S BACK.
HE'S EARLY.
- TENCHI, I MISSED YOU SO MUCH!
- WELCOME HOME.
- RYOKO, TAKE YOUR HANDS OFF
LORD TENCHI THIS INSTANT.
- IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
BESIDES,
TODAY'S THE ANNIVERSARY
OF THE DAY TENCHI
AND I FIRST MET.
- YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO MET HIM THAT DAY.
- COME ON, TENCHI, PARTY!
PARTY!
- ( all laughing )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( screeches )
- HI, I'M TENCHI MASAKI.
I'M BACK HOME IN OKAYAMA NOW.
I DID SOMETHING REALLY TERRIBLE
ON A SPECIAL DAY TWO YEARS AGO.
I WAS WEARING A NECKLACE
MY MOTHER HAD GIVEN ME,
A VERY SPECIAL
AND MAGICAL NECKLACE,
RYOKO AND EVERYONE ELSE
WOULD HAVE BEEN A LOT BETTER OFF
IF I HADN'T BEEN WEARING IT,
BUT THEN AGAIN,
I WOULD NEVER HAVE MADE FRIENDS
WITH SIX AMAZING GIRLS
ALL AT ONCE, EITHER.
THE NEXT EPISODE
OF THE NEW TENCHI MUYO SERIES...
"TENCHI ANNIVERSARY."