- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ♪ THERE YOU GO ♪
- ( meowing in rhythm )
♪ THERE YOU GO ♪
♪ ONE, TWO, THREE ♪
- ♪ THERE YOU GO ♪
- ( meowing in rhythm )
- ( laughing )
♪ ONE, TWO, THREE ♪
♪ THERE YOU GO ♪
- HUH?  HMM?
( screaming )
- ( laughing )
- OH, RYOKO,
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
( crying )
- ( shrieks )
- COME ON, QUIET DOWN.  HAS
EVERYBODY GONE BONKERS IN HERE?
HMM?
- ( shouts )
- RYOKO'S APPLIED MAKEUP
TO HER FACE BY THE POUND.
( laughing maniacally )
- ( growls )
HEY, YOU, WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
- ( muttering ) I DON'T KNOW.
- ( all laughing )
- ( growls )
CUT IT OUT!
I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
- WAS IT SOMETHING WE SAID?
- All: OH!
- ( chattering )
- WOW!  WHAT A TERRIFIC MOVE.
LET'S TRY IT.
- RIGHT.  HERE IT GOES.
- ( grunting )
- HMM.
- HUH?
- I THINK I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
ALL THEY CAN TALK ABOUT
IS CARS AND WRESTLING.
- AND WHAT'S REALLY STUPID
IS THEY DON'T KNOW A LOT
ABOUT EITHER SUBJECT.
- ( girls laughing )
- FROM NOW ON, I'M ONLY
GOING TO DATE BOYS
AT LEAST
TWO YEARS OLDER THAN ME.
- WHAT ARE YOU STARING AT?
BETTER TELL US RIGHT NOW.
- I'LL BRING YOU DOWN!
- HEY, CUT IT OUT!
I'M NOT TELLING YOU ANYTHING.
LET ME GO!
- Girl: OOH, LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S SUPER CUTE.
- Girl #2:
NAH, HE'S TOO CLEAN CUT.
I LIKE GUYS WHO HAVE
SOME KIND OF WILD LOOK.
MAYBE AN EARRING OR TATTOO.
- WELL, THEN HOW ABOUT THAT ONE
RIGHT THERE?
- NO, THAT GUY LOOKS
JUST LIKE A MONKEY.
- IT HAPPENS THAT MONKEY LOOKS
ARE VERY "IN" AT THE MOMENT.
- Both: HUH?  NO WAY!
- TURN THE PAGE.  MAYBE
THE CHOICES WILL BE BETTER.
- IT'S SO HARD FOR ME TO FIND
SOMEONE I'D REALLY LIKE.
- OH, NOW'S HERE'S ONE
I COULD LIKE A LOT.
- WELL, LET ME SEE.
- WOW!
- HEY, SAKUYA, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- HUH?
- YOU MUST HAVE A FAVORITE
TYPE OF GUY, TOO, RIGHT?
- OH, RIGHT.
RIGHT.  UH...
- All: TELL ME.
- ( laughs )
SOMEBODY WHO WAITS FOR ME,
I THINK.
SOMEBODY WHO WAITS FOR YOU?
(all:) WHATEVER DO
YOU MEAN BY THAT?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- ( laughs )
I'M AFRAID I DON'T UNDERSTAND
IT EITHER.  SORRY.
- I DO.
YOU'RE JUST BEING CHILDISH.
YOU KNOW,
YOU SHOULDN'T BE LIKE THAT.
- SHE'S RIGHT.
WE'RE NOT THAT YOUNG ANYMORE.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO WAIT AROUND.
- YEP, WE NEED TO TAKE DATING
INTO OUR OWN HANDS.
- I GUESS SO.
- LOOK WHAT I SEE.
THIS BOY IS MINE.
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
- I DON'T THINK HE'S SO BAD.
- WE REALLY HAD YOU GOING THERE
FOR A WHILE DIDN'T WE, BUDDY?
- NEXT TIME TRY YOUR HEAD HOLD
ON SOMEBODY ELSE.
- ( sighs )
- HMM?  WONDER WHO CALLED.
- You have two messages.
- ( beeps )
- Ryoko: Hi, Tenchi, it's me.
- ( gasps )
- I wanna go on a date
with you this Sunday.
Now don't you dare tell that
little fool Ayeka about this.
Meet me in Station Park at noon.
See you then.
- And if you don't show up,
you know what'll happen.
Bye-bye.
- OH, BOY, DO I.
- Hi, Tenchi.  It's Sakuya.
- HUH?
I'm calling to see if you
would like to take a walk
in Station Park this weekend
if the weather's nice.
So let me know
if you're interested, okay?
Bye for now.
- ( beeps )
- ( groaning )
( sighs )
- TENCHI!
YOU BETTER MAKE SURE
YOU SHOW UP, TENCHI!
( howling )
- ( moans )
JUST AS I SHOULD HAVE EXPECTED,
RYOKO'S RUNNING LATE.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
I DON'T BELIEVE I'VE EVER
GONE OUT ANYWHERE WITH RYOKO
ALONE BEFORE TODAY.
- TENCHI.
- OH!  YOU'RE LATE.
- OH!
- I'M SORRY.
BUT I'M HERE NOW, TENCHI.
HAVE YOU MISSED ME?
I'LL MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
WE'LL SPEND THE WHOLE DAY
TOGETHER, ALL RIGHT?
AREN'T YOU HAPPY, TENCHI?
- I'M OKAY, I GUESS.
- ( laughing )
WELL, COME ON, SAY SOMETHING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I LOOK PRETTY TODAY, RIGHT?
- RYOKO, WHAT'S HAPPENED TO YOU?
- OH, YOU NAUGHTY BOY.
YOU HAVE THAT BACKWARDS.
YOU MEAN WHAT IS
GOING TO HAPPEN TO US.
- ( boy laughing )
- ( boy mocking )
- ( crowd murmuring )
- Ryoko: HUH?
WHAT'S EVERYBODY GAWKING AT?
BEAT IT!  BUZZ OFF!
( shrieks )
DON'T WORRY, TENCHI.  WE'RE
ALONE.  IT'S JUST YOU AND ME.
NOW LET'S GO VISIT
ALL THE FASHIONABLE "IN" SPOTS.
- DON'T CLING SO TIGHT, OKAY?
MY NECK CAN'T TAKE IT.
- ALL RIGHT, GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
HERE WE GO, TENCHI.
- ( laughs )
- Ryoko: GIVE ME ANOTHER ONE!
- I DON'T GET WHY THIS SPOT
IS ON THE "IN" LIST.
- YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
BEEF BOWL RESTAURANTS
ARE VERY TRENDY RIGHT NOW.
LOOK AROUND YOU.
- IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
- HERE.
COME ON, OPEN WIDE.  AHHH!
- ALL RIGHT, HIROSHI, DO IT!
- OKAY, JUST WATCH.
( grunts ) YES!
- THAT'S REAL PUNCHING POWER.
WOW!
- HUH?
- TAKE THIS, AYEKA!
- Hiroshi: WOW!
- NOW THAT'S POWER, FRIEND.
( shouts )
- I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
- WHAT DID I DO?
LET GO.  YOU'RE HURTING ME.
- ( both gasp )
- WHAT'S THE BIG RUSH ANYWAY?
- ( laughing )
- WHAT DID YOU SEE?
- YOU ARE TOO MUCH!
- ( chattering )
- RYOKO, THERE ARE TOO MANY
AHEAD OF US.
WE'LL NEVER GET IN.
HUH?
- TENCHI!  TENCHI, OVER HERE.
THERE'S NO LINE AT ALL,
AND LOOK WHAT THEY OFFER.
- THEY TAKE PHOTO IDs?
- ( camera shutter clicking )
- HA HA!
( vocalizes )
OH, YEAH!
Ryoko:
YOU CAN'T DO THIS TO ME!
HOW DARE YOU MESS
WITH MY PERFORMANCE!
- COME ON, RYOKO, STOP IT!
- I WON'T BE COMING BACK.
YOU HEAR ME?!
- HEY, THAT'S ENOUGH.
- Girl: HONEY, WAIT UP!
WAIT FOR ME!
- ( meows )
- LET'S GO TO THE NEXT SPOT,
SHALL WE?
- LET'S NOT.
- HOW COME?
IT'S BEEN A LOT OF FUN SO FAR.
- OH, YEAH?
WELL, MAYBE FOR YOU.
- YOU SHOULD TRY TO ENJOY
YOURSELF MORE.  HOW ABOUT IT?
- I REALLY DON'T THINK SO.
- HAVING FUN.
ISN'T THAT ALL THAT MATTERS?
- NO, THAT'S WRONG.
- CAN'T YOU PRETEND IT'S RIGHT?
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
- THIS IS STUPID.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH.  HUH?
- Sasami:
RYOKO, WHERE ARE YOU?  RYOKO.
ARE YOU IN THERE?
COME ON, ANSWER ME.
I'M COMING IN NOW.
IT'S ME.
HUH?
"COLOR YOUR ROMANTIC EVENING.
PUT LOVE ON YOUR LIPS
WITH NIGHT PEARL ROUGE."
OH!
WOW!  IT'S LOVELY.
- HMM.  HEY, WHY ARE YOU
STANDING THERE, STARING AT ME?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
RYOKO'S WEARING MAKEUP.
( laughing )
- WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING
WHEN YOU LOOK A ME?
JUST WHAT'S SO AMUSING?
- NOTHING.
- I DEMAND TO KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.  HUH?
- ALL RIGHT,
WHERE ARE WE GOING NEXT?
- HMM?
- GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
- TENCHI.
- ( sighs )
IT WAS NO BIG DEAL.
I MEAN, HE JUST TOOK MY HAND.
- ( sighs )
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
COME OVER ME.
I DON'T SEEM TO BE ACTING
LIKE MYSELF RIGHT NOW.
- ( screams )
- ( laughing )
- NOT FUNNY!
- ( gasps )
TENCHI.
- HERE.
- I'M TOO UPSET.
I'M NOT THIRSTY ANYMORE.
- IS THERE ANY OTHER PLACE
YOU'D LIKE TO VISIT?
- UH... HMM.
WELL, YES, OF COURSE THERE IS.
- OKAY.
- WHY DON'T WE MAKE
IT ANOTHER TIME?
IT'S GETTING LATE.
- HUH?
I GUESS I REALLY HAD
TOO MUCH FUN TODAY.
- RYOKO, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- WELL, THINGS TO DO.
GOTTA GO NOW.
LET'S DO THIS AGAIN.
SEE YOU.
GOOD NIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
BYE-BYE.
- GOSH, SHE'S SURE SELFISH.
AND UNPREDICTABLE.
YET, SOMEHOW I'M ATTRACTED
TO HER.
SHE WAS KIND OF CUTE TONIGHT.
- Sakuya: TENCHI.
- HUH?
IT'S YOU, SAKUYA.
- HERE YOU GO.
- SHE MUST HAVE BEEN HANGING OUT
IN THE PARK ALL DAY LONG
WAITING FOR ME.
- it's Sakuya.  I'm calling
to see if you would like
to take a walk
in Station Park this weekend,
if the weather is nice.
So let me know
if you're interested, okay?
Bye for now.
- UGH!
I'M SORRY, SAKUYA.
- ( sobbing )
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN THINKING,
TRYING TO COME UP
WITH SOMETHING,
TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT I DID WRONG.
- LISTEN, YOU DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING WRONG.
- YOU SEE, I KNOW I'M KIND OF
NOISY AND A LITTLE BIT HYPER.
- BUT THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- AND I DON'T HAVE
THE GREATEST FIGURE EITHER.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- AND I CAN'T COOK.
I BURN EVERYTHING.
- WHAT POINT ARE YOU TRYING
TO MAKE?
- LIFE IS KIND OF...
STRANGE MOST TIMES,
ISN'T IT?
FOR A LONG TIME NOW,
I'VE BEEN SEEING
THIS ONE IMAGE.
- HUH?
- ON MY WAY HOME FROM SCHOOL,
AS I'M WALKING ALONE THROUGH
THE CAMPUS GROUNDS AT DUSK,
I SEE THE LONG SHADOW
OF SOMEONE WAITING FOR ME.
OR IT COULD JUST BE ME
WAITING FOR YOU.
I AM ALONE,
BUT IN THE COMPANY OF THIS IMAGE
I AM NOT LONELY.
I ANTICIPATE THE TENDER MOMENT
WHEN I'LL BE HOLDING
THIS SPECIAL SOMEONE
WHO IS WAITING FOR ME.
I'VE DREAMED OF THIS
FOR A LONG TIME NOW.
AN IMAGE HAS ALWAYS
BEEN PRESENT,
BUT NOW I KNOW FOR SURE,
IT'S NOT YOU.
TENCHI, YOU'RE NOT
WAITING FOR ME.
I SEE VERY CLEARLY NOW
YOU ALREADY HAVE SOMEONE
WHO'S WAITING FOR YOU.
- SAKUYA, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG.
I CAN EXPLAIN.
- LIAR.
- WHAT?
- I CAN TELL WHEN YOU'RE LYING
BECAUSE YOUR NOSE BEGINS
TO TWITCH AND DON'T BOTHER
TO COVER IT UP.
I'VE ALREADY SEEN IT.
- UH... HUH?
- YOU KNOW, YOU'RE REALLY
A LOUSY LIAR, TENCHI.
- I'M NOT LYING!  HUH?
- ( sobbing )
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I'M SORRY I LAID
ALL THIS STUFF ON YOU.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE BOTHERED YOU.
SEE YOU AROUND, BYE.
( grunts )
- ( laughing )
- all: WHOA!
- SHE ISN'T HER MOODY SELF.
I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED TO HER.
- DEFINITELY STRANGE.
- IS IT THE END OF THE CENTURY?
- IT MUST HAVE BEEN AWFULLY GOOD
WHATEVER IT WAS THAT HAPPENED.
- SHE'S WAY TOO CHEERY,
AND I DON'T LIKE IT AT ALL.
- AYEKA, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU TODAY?
WHY ARE YOU MAKING FACES, HUH?
- NOTHING'S WRONG.
- OKAY, I'LL GO ALONG WITH THAT.
HERE YOU GO.  YOU CAN HAVE SOME
OF MY OMELET IF YOU'D LIKE.
OKAY?
- ( all gasp )
- WHAT?
- HUH?
- ( screeches )
- NO, THANK YOU, I JUST ATE--
- ( Ryoko laughing )
- ( Ayeka mumbling )
- IT'S FOR YOU.
- ( screaming )
- ( laughs )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meowing )
- HI, I'M SASAMI.
RYO-OHKI
HAS BEEN SO NAUGHTY LATELY.
OH, NO, NOW LOOK WHAT
YOU'VE DONE, RYO-OHKI!
YOU KNOW, GRANDFATHER
TREASURES THIS STATUE.
YOU CAN'T JUST BREAK IT
AND THEN THINK YOU CAN
GET AWAY WITH IT.
IT ONLY MAKES IT WORSE
IF YOU TRY TO LIE ABOUT IT.
OH, I REALLY DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO WITH YOU ANYMORE.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF THE NEW
"TENCHI MUYO" SERIES--
"MOON MISSION."