- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
HORRIBLE!  YUCK.  PHOOEY.
DREADFUL.  TERRIBLE.
I AM TELLING YOU,
THIS STUFF IS BAD.
- YES, IT'S RATHER SALTY,
HONORABLE FATHER.
- I'M SORRY, FATHER,
BUT THIS ISN'T EVEN EDIBLE.
THERE'S EGGPLANT IN IT.
- HEY, STOP COMPLAINING.
MR. MASAKI HAS GONE OUT
OF HIS WAY TO COOK THIS FOR US.
WITH SASAMI ON THE SICK LIST,
WE SHOULD BE GRATEFUL
JUST TO HAVE FOOD.
- ON A SCALE OF ONE TO TEN,
YOU BLEW IT.
SORRY, NOBUYUKI.
- OLD MAN, COOK IT AGAIN
AND MAKE IT MORE SALTY.
- PLEASE MAKE IT LESS SALTY.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
MISO SOUP IS NO GOOD
UNLESS IT'S SALTY ENOUGH
TO MAKE YOUR MOUTH TWIST UP.
- HA!  THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I EXPECTED AN UNCIVILIZED
COUNTRY BUMPKIN
LIKE YOU WOULD SAY.
- BETTER WATCH YOUR MOUTH,
MISSY.
HOW DARE YOU CHALLENGE
MY TASTE BUDS.
I WON THE GOLD MEDAL AT
THE PIRATE GOURMET COMPETITION.
JUST YOU LOOK.
I'M A REAL FOOD EXPERT.
HA!  THE BEST FOOD YOU'VE
TASTED IS THE MEALS
YOU ATE BEHIND BARS
IN GALAXY PRISON.
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS YOU'RE
1,000 YEARS BEHIND ME.
I'M A THREE STAR GOURMET
OF THE JURAI ROYAL FAMILY.
- ( both grunting )
I'M THE EXPERT!
- TOO SALTY!
- TOO BLAND!
- SALTY!
- BLAND!
( grunting )
- STOP IT!  BACK OFF!
- THE EGGPLANT'S YUCKY!
- ( sighs )
- ( shouting )
- ( crashing )
- GET UP.  MUST MAKE DINNER
AND SWEEP THE HOUSE.
MUSTN'T LET THE LAUNDRY
PILE UP.
I REALLY GOTTA GET
MY HOUSEWORK DONE.
SO MUCH TO DO.
- ( whimpers )
- TOO SALTY.
- BLAND AND THAT'S FINAL.
- TOO MUCH EGGPLANT!
- ( dishes clanking )
- ( vacuum cleaner whirring )
- ( snoring )
- ( sneezes )
- AGH!
( thinking ) I ENVY CLOUDS.
THEY'RE SO FREE.
THEY JUST FLOAT AROUND.
I'M TIRED, HONEY.
I NEED TO GET AWAY
FOR A WHILE.
I CAN'T HELP BUT WONDER
HOW TENCHI IS DOING.
I THINK I'D BETTER LOOK IN
ON HIM, DEAR.
- Sakuya:
I SEE CLEARLY NOW.
YOU ALREADY HAVE SOMEONE
WAITING FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE REALLY
A LOUSY LIAR, TENCHI.
GOODBYE, TENCHI.
- ( sighs )
- HMM.
HOW IN THE WORLD
WILL I EVER FIND MY BOY?
- MATORI.
- I KNOW WHO YOU MEAN.
I SEE HIM.
TENCHI'S FATHER.
- ( laughs )
- WELL, HERE WE GO.
- OH!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, SIR?
- I'M FINE, THANK YOU.  AGH!
- OH, MY.
YOU'RE MR. MASAKI, AREN'T YOU?
- THERE.  NOW I CAN SEE YOU.
DO I KNOW YOU FROM SOMEWHERE?
- YES, YOU DO.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU AGAIN.
- DON'T TELL ME.
YOUR NAME IS...
WAIT.  IT'LL COME TO ME.
- I KNOW YOUR SON.
- OF COURSE.  THAT'S IT.
YOU'RE TENCHI'S FRIEND.
WHAT A COINCIDENCE
MEETING YOU
HERE IN THE MIDDLE
OF THIS GREAT BIG CITY.
ARE YOU FAMILIAR
WITH THIS NEIGHBORHOOD?
- AS A MATTER OF FACT, I AM.
- I WISH I HAD TIME TO TALK.
BUT I'M TRYING
TO FIND TENCHI'S APARTMENT.
WOULD YOU BE ABLE
TO SHOW ME THE WAY?
- OF COURSE, IF YOU WISH.
- HEY, I REMEMBER NOW.
YOUR NAME,
IT'S SAKUYA SHIROKUMA.
- NOT QUITE.
- WHAT THEN?
- IT'S ACTUALLY KUMASHIRO.
- ( laughs )
- ( doorbell rings )
- Tenchi: BE RIGHT THERE.
( gasps ) DAD, IS THAT YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I HAD TO COME TO TOKYO
ON SOME IMPORTANT BUSINESS.
SO I THOUGHT I'D STOP BY
AND SURPRISE YOU.
- HOW'D YOU FIND ME?
- I GOT SOME GREAT HELP.
- SAKUYA BROUGHT YOU?
- I'M STARVING.
- I WONDER WHERE
OUR NOBLE FATHER'S GONE.
- KIYONE, COME ON,
YOU GOTTA GET UP NOW.
- HEY, AYEKA, GET ME SOME FOOD.
- WHY SHOULD I?
THERE'S NO ONE TO COOK IT.
- GO COOK IT YOURSELF.
- WHY SHOULD I DO THAT?
- BECAUSE I SAID SO.
- MONKEY BREATH,
HOLD YOUR TONGUE.
- ( stomachs rumble )
- HUH?
- ( both sigh )
- I'VE AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T WE GO TO A RESTAURANT?
- MM-HMM.
- ( clears throat )
- ( thinking )
THIS SILENCE IS DEAFENING.
I WONDER WHAT'S MAKING
THEM SO UNCOMFORTABLE.
IS IT ME?
MAYBE I SHOULD LEAVE THEM ALONE.
IT CAN ONLY BE ONE THING.
THEY'RE IN LOVE.
NOW THAT I FIGURED IT OUT,
IT'S UP TO ME THE MATURE GROWNUP
TO HELP THESE YOUNG PEOPLE
COMMUNICATE.
THE FIRST THING I'VE GOT TO DO
IS GET THEM TO LOOSEN UP.
SO THEY FEEL RELAXED.
I'LL SET AN EXAMPLE
AND SHOW THEM HOW RELAXED
I AM MYSELF.
- ( clears throat )
- HUH?
- HEY, HOW ABOUT THIS YEAR'S
CHAMPIONSHIP BASEBALL GAMES?
DIMMIDANGO HIGH SCHOOL'S
BEEN DOING GREAT.
RIGHT UP THERE WITH THE BEST.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THEM
PLAY THAT FINAL GAME
AGAINST ONIGAJIMA HIGH SCHOOL.
- WELL, THAT WENT OVER
LIKE A LEAD BALLOON.
THEY'RE STARING AT ME
LIKE I JUST ESCAPED
FROM THE BOOBY HATCH.
I NEED A DIFFERENT TOPIC.
SOMETHING THAT'S TRENDY,
COOL, HIP.
SOMETHING YOUNG PEOPLE
THEIR AGE CAN RELATE TO.
( clears throat )
WELL, IT'S FASHIONABLE TO MEET
AT THE HACHIKO STATUE.
( laughs )
( gasps )
WHAT DOES THE STATUE OF HACHIKO
HAVE TO DO WITH THEM?
I'M MAKING A FOOL OF MYSELF.
I KNOW.  I'LL WARM 'EM UP
WITH A RIDDLE.
WHAT'S BLACK AND WHITE
AND READ ALL OVER?
IT'S A NEWSPAPER.
- ( laughs weakly )
- HMM.
- TOUGH AUDIENCE.
I'M DYING HERE.
SORRY, GUYS.
I'LL MAKE MYSELF USEFUL
AND GET SOME COLD DRINKS.
- I LOVE THAT OLD MAN
FOR TRYING.
I THINK I CAN USE HIM.
- ( growls )
- WE'RE NOT TRYING TO STEAL IT
FROM YOU.
WE JUST WANNA BORROW IT
SO THAT WE CAN ALL GO OUT
AND GET SOMETHING TO EAT.
SEE?
- WE'LL GIVE IT RIGHT BACK.
WE PROMISE.
- PLEASE, WE'RE BEGGING YOU.
- ( grumbles )
- YOU LITTLE BRAT.  I'M NOT
GONNA ASK YOU NICELY FOREVER.
UNDERSTAND ME?
( cracks knuckles )
GIVE ME THAT!
- ( explosion )
- ( Ryo-Ohki screeches )
- ( Ryoko winces )
- ( thudding )
- OH!
- WOW.  YOU'VE GROWN
QUITE STRONG, RYO-OHKI.
YOU MUST BE WORKING OUT.
- SORRY WE BOTHERED YOU,
RYO-OHKI.
- I MUST DO LAUNDRY
AND MAKE SUPPER.
CLEAN UP THE HOUSE.
- I DON'T SEEM TO BE DOING
ANY BETTER HERE HELPING TENCHI
THAN I DID BACK HOME
HELPING THE GIRLS.
ISN'T THERE ANYTHING
I CAN DO, DEAR WIFE?
- I WILL MORPH THIS
INTO SOMETHING VERY USEFUL.
YOU HAVE BEEN CREATED OUT
OF THE SUBCONSCIOUS MIND
OF A FATHER WHO WANTS
TO HELP HIS SON FIND TRUE LOVE.
YOU ARE PSEUDO DAD.
- I SEE.
- HERE'S YOUR JOB.
YOU ARE TO PLAY CUPID.
YOUR ASSIGNMENT IS TO CONNECT
THESE TWO YOUNG LOVERS
AND BRING THEM TOGETHER.
- A LOVE MACHINE?
- YOU MAY CHOOSE YOUR OWN WAY
TO ACCOMPLISH YOUR MISSION.
- I'M READY FOR LOVE.
I'M NOT FINISHED WITH YOU.
COME BACK.
- I'M ON A LOVE MISSION!
- ( meows )
- I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO THINK OF SOMETHING TO SAY.
ANYTHING.
- TENCHI, I'M IMPOSING.
YOU SHOULD BE SPENDING
THIS TIME WITH YOUR FATHER.
I'M SORRY.
- PLEASE DON'T BE.
MY FATHER IMPOSED ON YOU
TO BRING HIM HERE.
- NOT AT ALL.
YOUR FATHER'S A FUNNY FELLOW.
- THAT'S FOR SURE.
I WONDER WHAT'S KEEPING
HIM SO LONG.
I MIGHT AS WELL MAKE US
SOME COFFEE WHILE WE WAIT.
BE RIGHT BACK.
- OH!
- I'M SORRY,
BUT I HAVE TO GO NOW.
- WHAT?
- ( Sakuya gasps )
- HMM.
- ( Sakuya screaming )
- ( speaking gibberish )
WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU DOING?
- I WANT YOU TO BE MINE.
I'M IN LOVE.  I'M IN LOVE.
I'M IN LOVE...
- IDIOT.  YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO FALL IN LOVE WITH HER.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
YOU SHOULD HAVE WAITED
FOR MY INSTRUCTION.
- I WANT SOME FOOD.
- I WANT A GOOD MEAL.
- I WANT EGGPLANT!
I MUST BE CRAZY WITH HUNGER.
- I'M IN LOVE.  I'M IN LOVE.
I'M IN LOVE.  I'M IN LOVE.
I'M IN LOVE!
OH, YEAH!
I'M IN LOVE.
- HUH?
- LOVE, LOVE, LOVE, LOVE.
- OH, NO!
I WANT YOU TO BE MINE.
I DON'T.  MNH-MNH.
- ALL RIGHT, YEAH!
OOH!
I WANT YOU TO BE MINE.
- WHAT?  OH.
I'M NOT AVAILABLE.
- SHE SURE IS.
- I'M IN LOVE.  I'M IN LOVE.
YEAH!  HUH?
I WANT YOU TO BE MINE.
- NO WAY, YOU CREEP.
- HUH?
- CHILL OUT, DUDE.
- I'M IN LOVE.  I'M IN LOVE.
I'M IN LOVE.  I'M IN LOVE.
- Nobuyuki: I'M BACK.
HMM?
- Tenchi's voice:
DAD, I'VE GONE OUT
TO LOOK FOR SAKUYA.
MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME
AND HAVE SOME TEA.
I'LL BE BACK SOON.
- HMM.  IT'S GREAT TO BE YOUNG
AND IN LOVE, RIGHT, DEAR?
- Matori: WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING,
YOU SLOW-WITTED NUMBSKULL?
WHO TOLD YOU TO RUN OFF
WITH EVERY PRETTY
FEMALE IN YOUR PATH? HUH?
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE YOU COULD
BE COMPLETELY STUPID.
NOW I WANT YOU
TO PAY ATTENTION.
YOUR MISSION IS TO HELP GET
THOSE TWO PEOPLE TOGETHER.
UNDERSTAND?
- POSSIBLY.
- I DON'T LIKE MISTAKES.
YOU BEST GET IT RIGHT.
- I WILL.
- DON'T FORGET.
IF YOU FAIL ME AGAIN, I WILL
BLOW YOU AWAY, PSEUDO DAD.
- I GOT IT.
- WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
GET TO WORK.
- YES, DEAR.  WILL YOU BE MINE?
- OH!  GET OUT OF HERE!
I'M IN LOVE!
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY
TO HER.
I DIDN'T HAVE A CLUE
THE LAST TIME.
BUT I'LL BE HISTORY
FOR SURE THIS TIME
IF I DON'T THINK OF SOMETHING.
- ( sighs )
I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT I CAN'T FORGET HIM.
- ( Pseudo Dad
speaking gibberish )
- HUH? ( gasps )
- DAD, IS THAT YOU?
- HA HA!
I'M IN LOVE, SON.
- NOT WITH HER.
PUT HER DOWN.
YOU'RE NOT HIM.
YOU IMPOSTOR!
RELEASE HER RIGHT NOW.
I'M NOT GONNA ASK YOU AGAIN.
COME BACK HERE, YOU!
PUT HER DOWN!
- I GUESS THAT'S THE BEST
I CAN EXPECT FROM HIM.
WELL, MIGHT AS WELL
LET HIM RUN WILD.
AT LEAST HE'LL KEEP
THE BOY BUSY.
LET HIM DO HIS BEST.  THE REAL
FATHER WILL FINISH THE JOB.
( laughing )
- BAD OMEN.
HUH?  HMM?  OH!
I WONDER.  MAYBE SOMETHING
HAPPENED TO TENCHI.
- RELEASE HER.
- NO.  I LOVE HER.
- ( gasps ) TENCHI, IT'S YOU.
- TAKE YOUR ARM OFF HER
RIGHT NOW!
- LOVE, LOVE LOVE!
- PLEASE, LET HIM GO.
- HE HAS TO BE AROUND HERE
SOMEWHERE.
TENCHI, IF YOU CAN HEAR ME,
SAY SOMETHING.
- ( grunting )
- HELP, SOMEBODY, PLEASE.
- ( panting ) TENCHI!
HANG ON, SON!
TENCHI AND MISS SHIROKUMA
ARE IN TERRIBLE TROUBLE.
THEY'VE BEEN CAPTURED
BY A GREAT BIG UGLY MONSTER.
- MY DAD.
- MY NAME IS KUMASHIRO.
- I'M IN LOVE AND LOVE WINS OUT
OVER EVERYTHING.
- NOT YOUR KIND OF LOVE.
YOU'VE COME HERE
TO DISTURB
THE EARTH'S PEACE.
IN THE NAME OF THE GREAT REASON
THAT RULES THIS PLANET,
I MUST DEFEAT YOU.
- DAD, HOW CAN YOU DO THAT?
- DON'T YOU WORRY, TENCHI.
BECAUSE I AM THE SON
OF A SHRINE KEEPER,
AND ALL SHRINES HAVE A WEAPON
TO DESTROY EVIL DEMONS.
NOW WATCH!
ANYBODY THERE?
- WELCOME TO SAKIRA TENMANGU
SHRINE.  HOW MAY I HELP YOU?
- I NEED A DEMON DESTROYER
ARROW PLEASE.
NOW TAKE THIS!  AGH!
- DAD, I REALLY DON'T THINK
THAT'S GOING TO WORK.
- ( screaming )
I'M FINISHED.  YOU SUCKED
THE LOVE RIGHT OUT OF ME.
- THAT LOVE DEMON TURNED OUT
TO BE JUST A GREAT BIG WIMP.
- LUCKY FOR US.
( sighs )
( groans )
- TENCHI, WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
- HMM?
- DON'T YOU HAVE SOMETHING
YOU WANT TO SAY TO SAKUYA?
- WELL, IF I KNEW WHAT
I WANTED TO SAY,
I WOULD HAVE SAID IT
A LONG TIME AGO.
- TENCHI,
THERE'S ALWAYS A WAY,
EVEN IF YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW OR WHAT.
YOU JUST SAY WHAT YOU REALLY
WANT TO SAY FROM THE HEART.
AND TELL HER WHAT YOU
FEEL INSIDE.  HMM?
- HMM.
- I WAS NO ELOQUENT ROMEO
MYSELF,
BUT I DID MANAGE TO SAY WHAT
I HAD TO SAY TO YOUR MOTHER.
- YOU DID?  OH.
- GO ON, SON.
BEHAVE LIKE A MAN.
- MM-HMM.
- ( laughs )
- I WAS WORRIED.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, I'M FINE, THANKS.
- OH, GOOD.
- SAKUYA--
- I HAVE TO GO.
- WAIT.
THERE'S SOMETHING I'VE BEEN
MEANING TO TELL YOU.
YOU SEE, IT'S THE ANSWER.
I HAVEN'T TOLD YOU
MY ANSWER YET.
- ANSWER?
- TO YOUR QUESTION.
I WANTED TO TELL YOU THAT
I REALLY DON'T KNOW FOR SURE YET
IF I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU.
SO I STILL CAN'T GIVE YOU
ANY DEFINITE ANSWER
'CAUSE I DON'T WANNA LEAD
YOU ON AND GET YOUR HOPES UP,
BUT I WILL PROMISE YOU THIS.
I'LL FIND THE ANSWER IF YOU
CAN JUST GIVE ME MORE TIME.
- I'M SORRY.
I WISH--
- I'M HAPPY TO SEE YOUR NOSE
ISN'T TWITCHING TODAY.
- HMM?
- AT LEAST YOU'RE HONEST.
I HAVE TO BE
ON MY WAY HOME NOW.
- ALL RIGHT, SEE YOU.
- I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW THEN.
BYE, TENCHI.
I ALMOST FORGOT.  PLEASE BE SURE
AND THANK YOUR FATHER
FOR ME, WILL YOU?
- HUH?
THANKS, FATHER.
YOU'RE THE BEST. ( sighs )
- LOOKS LIKE THAT'S ABOUT IT,
AT LEAST FOR NOW.
- AND I SAY,
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
( laughs )
- I NEED FOOD HERE.
- A NICE MEAL.
- A HOT BATH HERE.
I MEAN, KIYONE,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- LAUNDRY, COOKING
AND CLEANING.
THOSE ARE THE CHORES THAT
HAVE TO BE TAKEN CARE OF.
I'D BETTER GET UP.
THERE'S SO MUCH TO DO.
( panting )
- ( meowing )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meowing )
- HI, I'M WASHU.
A MYSTERIOUS GIRL SHOWS UP
OUT OF THE BLUE
IN FRONT OF OUR VERY EYES.
HER NAME IS YUGI,
AND SHE IS INCREDIBLE.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
SHE'S SO POWERFUL,
SHE KNOCKED RYOKO OUT COLD
WITH ONE BLOW.
WITHOUT TENCHI AROUND
TO HELP US,
I DON'T THINK WE'LL SURVIVE.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF THE NEW
"TENCHI MUYO" SERIES--
"THE EYE OF THE DESTROYER."