- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- ( moaning slightly )
- SASAMI.
SASAMI!
- ( gasps )
IS THAT YOU, YUGI?
- YES.
WE'RE FRIENDS,
AREN'T WE, SASAMI?
- HUH?
( giggles )
SURE, YOU BET.
- HMM.
- ( gasps )
YUGI YUGI!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
( gasps ) YUGI!
- ( screeches )
- HUH HUH?
OH...
I WAS DREAMING
ABOUT YUGI AGAIN.
- ( meows )
- ( people talking,
laughing on TV )
- ( sighs ) NORMALLY THIS
IS MY FAVORITE FOOD.
NOODLES USUALLY HIT THE SPOT
IN THE SUMMERTIME.
BUT TODAY THEY JUST TASTE
KINDA BLAH.
- Man on TV: GET OUT OF HERE,
AND PACK YOUR BAGS, BUD.
- Man on TV #2:
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THE ONLY BAGS I OWN
ARE UNDER MY EYES!
- ( knocking )
- HUH?
- Man on TV:
WELL, WHEN I'M DONE WITH YOU...
- WASHU?
- OH.  ( chuckles )
- WHAT?
NOW YOU COME OUT?
- LONG TIME NO SEE.
DID YOU MISS ME, PRINCESS?
- WHILE YOU'VE BEEN
LOCKED UP IN THERE...
...TERRIBLE THINGS HAVE BEEN
HAPPENING OUT HERE!
RYOKO'S GONE BACK
TO OUTER SPACE
TO LIVE THE LIFE OF
A SPACE PIRATE AGAIN!
WHAT'S WORSE IS MIHOSHI
AND KIYONE ARE IN SPACE TOO.
- AAH!
- AND TENCHI IS STILL IN TOKYO!
- I'VE GOT STUFF TO SHOW YOU.
- HUH?
- I'VE MADE SOME
IMPORTANT DISCOVERIES.
- ( laughing,
playful screaming )
- I GOT IT, I GOT IT!
- GET IT!
- HOT DOGS, NACHOS AND CHEESE.
- TIME FOR US
TO CATCH SOME RAYS.
- ( laughing )
- PASS IT OVER TO ME.
- AAH!
- TENCHI, WHAT ARE YOU
STARING AT?
- COME ON, I'M WATCHING
THE SCENERY.
- ( grunts )
- SORRY, BOYS, IT SLIPPED.
HEY, TENCHI, WHY DON'T YOU
COME AND JOIN US?
- EH...
- WELL?
( giggles )
- ( beeping )
- JUST TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
- I REMEMBER THAT GIRL.
- YES, WE BOTH DO.
THIS IS THAT AWFUL GIRL
NAMED YUGI WHO ATTACKED
THE MASAKI SHRINE.
- ( beeping rapidly )
- NOW DID YOU CATCH THAT?
- ( giggles bashfully )
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO SEE?
- HER ORGANIC ENERGY
HAD A TRACE OF JURAITRIUM 7000.
- WHAT IS THIS JURAI-TRIO STUFF?
HUH?
WOW.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
- JURAITRIUM 7000
IS THE ORGANIC ENERGY
POSSESSED BY ONLY JURAIANS.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT. YOU'RE
SAYING YUGI IS A JURAIAN
JUST LIKE MYSELF?
- IT SURE LOOKS THAT WAY.
- BUT THAT CAN'T BE POSSIBLE.
HOW WOULD OTHER JURAIANS
BESIDES US HAVE GOTTEN HERE?
- THAT'S WHAT I'D LIKE TO KNOW.
- NOBODY ON OUR PLANET IS
EVEN REMOTELY LIKE HER
IN ANY WAY. IF SHE'S HERE NOW,
HOW DID SHE COME TO EARTH?
- I HAVE AN IDEA.
DO YOU REMEMBER THOSE
OLD ROOMS IN OKUTAMA?
- ( gasps )
SURE DO.
YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
ASIDE FROM US,
THAT'S THE ONLY JURAIAN WE KNOW
WHO'S EVER BEEN TO EARTH.
- I NEED YOU TO GO BACK
TO THE RUINS AND CHECK OUT
SOMETHING FOR ME WHILE I
CONTINUE MY RESEARCH HERE.
- I'LL GET RIGHT ON IT.
THE SOONER WE FIND OUT
ABOUT HER, THE BETTER.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE
ALL RIGHT THERE, PRINCESS?
- SURELY THERE'S AN EASIER WAY
FOR YOU TO TRAVEL.
- THIS MISSION IS URGENT.
I CAN'T BE TOO CHOOSY
ABOUT THE WAY I GET THERE.
IT'S SO HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT YUGI'S FROM MY PLANET.
- PRINCESS, YOU'RE LOOKING
QUITE PALE.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO REST
A WHILE?
- I'M ALL RIGHT.
IT'S JUST THAT--
- WHAT?
- I'M HAVING A HARD TIME
WITH THE FACT
THAT THERE MAY BE SOMEONE ELSE
ON EARTH FROM JURAI.
AND I'M PUZZLED AS TO
WHY SHE WOULD WANT
TO ATTACK THE MASAKI SHRINE.
- THAT IS A GOOD QUESTION.
- WE DON'T HAVE A CLUE EITHER.
- THIS YUGI...
WHO IS SHE, REALLY?
- ( straining )
( laughs ) THIS IS TRULY THE
BEST WAY TO CHILL WATERMELONS.
DON'T YOU THINK?
- ( meows )
- GEE, BEFORE EVERYBODY
WENT AWAY,
A WATERMELON THIS SIZE
WOULDN'T HAVE LASTED LONG.
WANNA GO HOME NOW?
- ( meows sadly )
- ( both gasp )
- ( whimpers )
- OH...
- Both: HUH?
- OH!
- ( giggles )
- OH, WOW, YUGI!
- I'VE COME TO VISIT YOU.
I'VE MISSED YOU.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU BOTH DONE A GREAT JOB.
- THANK YOU, SIR.
I FEEL QUITE HONORED.
- I FEEL HONORED ALSO.
- THANKS TO YOUR HARD WORK,
WE WERE ABLE TO DISCOVER
AND DESTROY THE HIDEOUT OF THAT
TERRIBLE SPACE PIRATE, RYOKO,
AND ARREST MOST
OF HER HENCHMEN AS WELL.
- WOW!  FOR DOING ALL THAT,
YOU SHOULD BE THANKING US.
( chuckles )
- HMM...
- OH!
- ( laughter )
- KIYONE!
- OH, I'M GONNA GET YOU
FOR THAT.
- NO WAY!
- ( laughter )
- ( overlapping chatter )
- THIS IS WHY I WENT BACK
TO BEING A SPACE PIRATE--
SO I COULD DISRUPT THE WORLD
THAT NASTY BACKSTABBERS,
LIKE THE BOTH OF YOU,
WALK AROUND IN.
- WAIT, DON'T LEAVE!
WHAT ABOUT TENCHI?
IS THIS WHAT YOU REALLY WANT?
YOU'RE NEVER GOING
BACK TO EARTH?
- THAT'S HISTORY.
- WHAT'S HAPPENED TO US?
HOW DID WE BECOME
SUCH TERRIBLE ENEMIES?
- WE'D LIKE TO REWARD
YOUR ACCOMPLISHMENT.
- ( gasps slightly )
- AND ON THAT NOTE,
WE AT GALAXY POLICE HEADQUARTERS
ARE PREPARED TO OFFER YOU
THE POSITION YOU DESERVE--
CONTINGENT UPON
RYOKO'S ARREST, OF COURSE.
- WOW!  WHAT COULD THAT BE?
- REASSIGNMENT BACK
TO GALAXY HEADQUARTERS.
- Both:
WE'RE VERY GRATEFUL, SIR.
- GOSH, I'M NOT SURE
WHAT WE DID,
BUT I'LL BET YOU'RE THRILLED.
AM I RIGHT?
- UH...
- KIYONE?
- MIHOSHI AND KIYONE PLAYED
SUCH A DIRTY TRICK ON ME.
BUT I HAVE TO ADMIT,
THEY CRACK ME UP.
IT WAS A HOOT
GETTING THE BEST OF THEM
BEFORE THEY FIGURED OUT
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
- ( inaudible )
- IT WAS A LOT OF FUN
HANGING OUT WITH THEM AGAIN.
- WHAT'S UP?
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE IN A GOOD MOOD.
- AS MATTER OF FACT,
I AM.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M THINKING I SHOULD GO
VISIT EARTH ONCE IN A WHILE.
- HMM, YOU COULD.
BUT WHY WOULD WANT
TO GO BACK THERE?
UNLESS YOU'RE MISSING SOMEONE
THAT YOU MUST GO SEE.
- WHO'S THERE TO MISS, HUH?
( growls )
I'M NEVER GOING
TO GO BACK THERE!
WHY SHOULD I?
I'M RYOKO THE SPACE PIRATE.
I DON'T BELONG THERE.
IT'S THE BOONDOCKS!
- YOU ARE SO RIGHT.
( chuckles )
- ( giggling )
COME ON. JUMP IN, YUGI!
THE WATER'S GREAT.
- OKAY...
( gasps )
-  YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HMM.  IF I THAW OUT.
- ( laughs )
- ( shrieks )
- YOU KNOW, I JUST HAD
A DREAM ABOUT YOU.
AND THEN HERE YOU ARE--
YOU SHOW UP IN REAL LIFE.
IT'S SOME COINCIDENCE, HUH?
- YEAH.
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
I LOVE THE FOREST.
- ME TOO.
IT'S ONE OF MY FAVORITE PLACES.
IT REMINDS ME OF HOME,
PLANET JURAI.
- PLANET JURAI. I'D LIKE TO
LIVE IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
WITH YOU, SASAMI.
- WHAT?
- WE'RE FRIENDS, AREN'T WE?
WE SHOULD BE TOGETHER FOREVER.
- HUH?
YUGI...
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- ( meows )
- ( steady beeping )
- THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
THE ENERGY FLOW FROM JURAI TREE
HAS BEEN COMPLETELY CUT OFF.
- AND THAT'S WHY
IT BECAME UNSEALED.
- AZAKA, IS IT POSSIBLE
TO COLLECT ANY DATA
FROM THE CAPSULE'S
MEMORY BANKS?
- WE COULD TRY TO ACTIVATE THEM
WITH OUR OWN ENERGY.
- THEN TRY IT.
- Both: YES, MA'AM.
- WE ARE RECEIVING
SOME DATA NOW.
DATA HAS BEEN ASSIMILATED.
- LET'S TAKE A LOOK
AT WHAT WE GOT.
- IN THE 27TH YEAR OF
THE EMPRESS HINASE'S
REIGN OVER JURAI,
HORRIBLE EVIL POWERS
WERE AWAKENED
IN A SIX-YEAR-OLD MUTANT
AND UNLEASHED ON THE PLANET.
- IN THE 27TH YEAR
OF HINASE?
- ACCORDING TO INFORMATION
STORED IN MY DATA BANK,
THAT WAS THE SAME YEAR
THAT PLANET JURAI
WAS ALMOST ANNIHILATED.
- SO THE MUTANT WHO CAUSE D IT
ALL WAS SEALED UP IN HERE
TO PREVENT FURTHER DESTRUCTION?
- ( gasps )
- AWW.
( giggles )
- ( humming )
- ( birds chirping )
- OH...
- ( chuckles )
YOU KNOW WHAT, YUGI?
- WHAT?
- EVERYWHERE YOU LOOK
YOU CAN FIND LOTS OF FRIENDS.
- YAH!
- HMM, BUT REAL ONES?
- HUH?
- I HAVE BEEN
ALL ALONE FOR A LONG TIME.
I WAS SO LONELY
THAT I CREATED MY OWN FRIENDS.
- ( growls )
- ( screaming )
- COME ON, EVERYONE,
PLAYTIME!
- ( growling )
- ( laughing )
- USING HER
EXTRAORDINARY POWER,
THE MUTANT CAUSED GREAT CHAOS
THROUGHOUT THE PLANET OF JURAI.
NO SINGLE WARRIOR HAD STOPPED
HER DESTABILIZING FORCE.
- ( laughing )
( grunts )
( gasps )
OH...
STOP RIGHT NOW!
PLEASE DON'T KILL THEM!
STOP FIRING!
- EMPRESS HINASE EMPLOYED
HER OWN COLOSSAL POWER,
WHICH WAS FINALLY ABLE
TO MATCH THE MUTANT'S STRENGTH.
- I WAS JUST KIDDING AROUND!
PLEASE STOP IT RIGHT NOW!
AAH!
( screams )
NO, WAIT!
- FAIR AND NOBLE SPIRIT,
EMPOWER ME SO THAT I AM ABLE
TO PUT THIS EVIL ONE
INTO ETERNAL SLEEP.
- ( screaming )
LET ME GO!
AAH!
PLEASE DON'T!
I'M AFRAID OF THE DARK!
DON'T SHUT ME IN!
PLEASE STOP IT!
I'M SO SCARED.
DON'T LEAVE ME ALONE!
I DON'T WANNA BE ALONE!
- ( echoing )
- ( rumbling )
- POOR LITTLE CHILD.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
HOWEVER, YOUR POWER POSES
A GREAT DANGER TO US ALL.
I'M SO SORRY TO HAVE
TO DO THIS TO YOU...
BUT I DON'T HAVE
ANY OTHER CHOICE.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- EMPRESS HINASE
SEALED UP THE MUTANT.
AND TO BE CERTAIN THAT
THIS POWERFUL CHILD
WOULD NEVER AGAIN AWAKEN
AND THREATEN THE STABILITY
OF JURAI,
SHE EXILED HER
TO A REMOTE PART OF SPACE,
WHERE FEW PLANETS EXISTED.
- THE OUTER REACHES OF
SPACE MAY HAVE BEEN HER
ORIGINAL DESTINATION, BUT
SHE NEVER ARRIVED.
THE REALITY IS SHE FELL DOWN
TO EARTH SOMEHOW.
- ISN'T THAT A STRANGE
TWIST OF FATE?
- I'LL BET NOBODY EVER DREAMED
THAT 3500 YEARS LATER
WE WOULD ALL END UP
ON THE SAME PLANET.
AND THAT I WOULD BE
STANDING ON THE SPOT
WHERE THE SHRINE FELL.
- AAH.
- WHAT ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT?
- ( gasps )
- WHY DO YOU LOOK SO SAD, YUGI?
DID SOMETHING BAD
HAPPEN TO YOU, HUH?
- ( meows )
- IT MUST BE WRONG
TO CREATE YOUR OWN PLAYMATES.
- WHAT?
- BECAUSE WHEN I DID,
I WAS SEVERELY PUNISHED!
- ( gasps )
- MM...
- COME ON, CHEER UP!
NOW QUIT WORRYING.
NOBODY WILL EVER
BOTHER YOU HERE, YUGI.
- MEOW MEOW MEOW!
- YEAH, OKAY.
- YOU'VE CONFIRMED IT.
YUGI IS THE MUTANT
WHO WAS SEALED UP IN A CAPSULE
FOR MANY THOUSANDS
OF YEARS.
NOW WE FINALLY KNOW
WHAT WE'RE DEALING WITH HERE.
- BUT WHAT WE DON'T KNOW
IS WHY DID SHE ATTACK
THE MASAKI SHRINE.
WAS IT AN ACT OF REVENGE
AGAINST US JURAIANS?
- I DOUBT THAT'S
THE WHOLE STORY.
IT'S INTERESTING, THOUGH,
THAT YUGI AWOKE
FROM HER LONG SLEEP
ABOUT THE SAME TIME
AS TENCHI'S FAMILY
STARTED FALLING APART.
- UH-HUH.
- IT SEEMS HIGHLY UNLIKELY
THAT THIS IS SHEER COINCIDENCE.
- ( laughing )
LET'S GO TO THIS PLACE.
THEY HAVE
THE MOST AWESOME RIDE.
- UM, I'M A LITTLE AFRAID
OF THAT.
- GOSH, I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE SUCH A SCAREDY-CAT.
HOW ABOUT THIS THEN?
- HMM...
THE PARASITE MUSEUM.
- Both: HUH?
HUH?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK THAT WAS?
- I BETTER SEE.
AAH!  WASHU, IT'S YOU!
- YEP.
WHEN I FIXED THE TUNNEL,
THE EXIT COORDINATES GOT
ALL SCREWED UP.
( straining )
OOH!
- I KNOW HER. HOW COME SHE
ENDED UP IN YOUR TOILET?
- THERE'S NO TIME TO EXPLAIN.
TENCHI, I NEED YOU
TO COME BACK TO
OKAYAMA WITH ME.
- WHAT?
- HUH?
- THERE'S SOMETHING
VERY VERY FISHY GOING ON.
- AYEKA ALREADY
TOLD ME ABOUT THAT.
YOU'RE ALL GETTING
SCATTERED AROUND, RIGHT?
- AND IT HAPPENED
VERY QUICKLY.
TENCHI, AREN'T YOU CONCERNED?
- I THINK YOU'RE BOTH
OVERREACTING.
IT'S A MERE COINCIDENCE.
- AH-AH-AH.
WAS IT MERE COINCIDENCE
THAT SOMEBODY ATTACKED
THE MASAKI SHRINE?
- WHAT?!  WHO WOULD HAVE DONE
SUCH A THING, AND WHY?!
- LOOK, I'M AFRAID THAT'S
A VERY LONG STORY.
- ARE GRANDPA
AND THE OTHERS OKAY?
- THEY BARELY SURVIVED.
I THINK IT WAS MEANT ONLY
AS A NASTY THREAT.
- I'M GRATEFUL
EVERYONE'S ALL RIGHT.
- BUT WITHOUT A DOUBT,
SOMETHING IS HAPPENING
IN YOUR HOMETOWN.
SOMETHING TERRIBLE, I THINK.
WILL YOU COME BACK WITH ME?
- YEAH, OF COURSE.
- TENCHI.
- HUH?
- WAIT! I THOUGHT WE
TALKED ABOUT SPENDING
THE SUMMER TOGETHER.
YOU PROMISED
WE WOULDN'T LEAVE
EACH OTHER'S SIDE
THE WHOLE TIME!
- SORRY, BUT I HAVE TO GO.
WASHU, JUST LET ME
GET MY STUFF.
- ( gasps slightly )
( exhales )
OH!
- STOP IT!
- DON'T GO.
STAY WITH ME, TENCHI, PLEASE.
WE WERE MAKING
SO MANY PLANS.
- SAKUYA, I FEEL AWFUL--
- EVERYBODY SEEMS TO
BE MORE IMPORTANT
TO YOU THAN I AM!
- STOP! I'M NOT SAYING THAT.
BECAUSE IT'S NOT
LIKE THAT AT ALL.
- TENCHI, THANK GOODNESS
YOU'RE HERE!
MY GRANDFATHER'S BEEN HURT.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
WILL HE BE ALL RIGHT?
- HE HURT HIS HIP
WHEN WE FELL OFF HIS MOPED,
AND NOW HE CAN'T STAND UP.
AND THE PROBLEM IS THERE'S
A TRAFFIC SAFETY CEREMONY
THIS AFTERNOON.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO HOST IT.
CAN YOU COVER FOR HIM?
- WHAT?!  HOW CAN I PRETEND
TO BE HIM?
- YOU JUST ACT LIKE
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING,
AND EVERYTHING WILL
BE FINE. I CAN'T TELL THEM THAT
GRANDPA WON'T BE AT THE
TRAFFIC SAFETY FUNCTION
BECAUSE HE WAS IN A
TRAFFIC ACCIDENT.
- ( groaning )
I'M SORRY, BUT I CAN'T GO
WITH YOU.
MAYBE I'LL BE ABLE
TO CATCH UP WITH YOU SOON.
- YOU GOTTA DO
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
- COME ON, TENCHI!
HURRY!
- HANG ON.
LET ME GRAB MY JACKET.
- ( door closes )
- OH, WELL, IT'S PROBABLY
NOT CRITICAL FOR TENCHI
TO BE IN OKAYAMA RIGHT NOW.
IT WON'T CHANGE ANYTHING.
BESIDES, IT'LL BE A
WHILE UNTIL I FINISH
MY DATA ANALYSIS ANYWAY.
TIME TO GO.
GOTTA GET BACK TO WORK.
HUH?
HMM...
- IT'S GOTTEN VERY QUIET,
SASAMI.
- THAT'S BECAUSE
IT'S EVENING ALREADY.
EVERYONE'S PROBABLY GONE HOME.
- SASAMI?
- YEAH?
- YOU SHOULD MOVE TO MY PLACE.
WE COULD LIVE THERE TOGETHER.
- WHAT?
- THEY'RE ALL GONNA BE
GONE PRETTY SOON ANYWAY.
SO COME WITH ME.
WE'LL HAVE A WONDERFUL LIFE
TOGETHER.
IT'LL BE THE MOST PERFECT
FRIENDSHIP!
I JUST CAN'T WAIT.
- I'M SORRY,
BUT THAT'S A CRAZY IDEA.
- HUH?
- WE CAN'T POSSIBLY
LIVE ON OUR OWN.
AFTER ALL,
WE'RE STILL JUST CHILDREN.
- DON'T YOU DISAPPOINT ME!
- HUH?
AAH!
- ( growling )
- YUGI...
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO YOU?
YUGI.
- ( upbeat music playing )
- ( people singing in Japanese )
- YAH!
( growls )
( meows )
- Tenchi: SAKUYA, YOU'RE
INTO PHOTOGRAPHY NOW?
THAT'S A VINTAGE CAMERA
YOU HAVE THERE, ISN'T IT?
WELL, YOU'VE GOTTA BE CAREFUL
WITH THOSE OLD CAMERAS.
YOU LOOK THROUGH THE VIEWFINDER
AND PRESS THE SHUTTER AND BOOM--
THE PERSON PHOTOGRAPHED
LOSES HIS SOUL, THEY SAY.
WHAT?  WHERE DID I GET
THIS SILLY OLD JOKE?
WELL, IT WAS MY GRANDPA
WHO TOLD ME THAT.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF
THE NEW TENCHI MUYO SERIES...