- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( dings )
- I SEE THE SHIBUYA AREA.
BOY, IT LOOKS TINY
FROM UP HERE.
- HUH?
RYOKO.
( sighs )
- YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU JUST SAW A GHOST.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- NOTHING.
I'M FINE, REALLY.
- All: MMM.
- THE HOUSE SEEMS SO EMPTY
WITH EVERYBODY GONE.
I MISS KIYONE AND MIHOSHI.
THIS MIGHT SOUND ODD,
BUT I MISS RYOKO TOO.
- HOW IS THAT EVEN POSSIBLE?
I DON'T MISS HER A BIT.
IN FACT,
I'M EXTREMELY HAPPY
THAT THAT BARBARIAN
IS OUT OF MY FACE.
I WON'T GIVE HER
ANOTHER THOUGHT.
Ayeka: ( panting )
( gasps )
HMM.
( panting )
OH!
RYOKO?
OH?
( gasps )
WASHU?
KIYONE AND MIHOSHI TOO?
HUH?
SASAMI.
RYO-OHKI?
- Yugi: ( laughs )
( laughing )
- ( gasps )
OH!
( groans )
- ( laughs )
- ( screams )
( gasps )
WHAT A DREAM.
IT SEEMED SO
DISTURBINGLY REAL.
WHY CAN'T I SHAKE IT OFF?
I HAVE THIS UNEASY FEELING
THAT SOMETHING AWFUL
IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
- Tsugaru:
PEACEFUL NIGHT, ISN'T IT?
- ( gasps )
- HI, PRINCESS.
WE MEET AGAIN.
SURPRISED, AREN'T YOU?
- YES, YOU SCARED ME.
- IT'S QUIET.
ALMOST FEELS LIKE
THE CALM BEFORE THE STORM.
BETTER WATCH OUT.
DREAMS CAN COME TRUE.
- WHAT?
Ayeka: WAS MY DREAM
A PREMONITION?
- I HAVE TO GO NOW.
BUT I'LL SEE YOU
AROUND SOMETIME.
COUNT ON IT.
TAKE CARE.
- PLEASE WAIT UP.
YOU NEVER TOLD ME YOUR NAME.
WHAT IS THIS ALL ABOUT?
WHY ARE YOU WARNING ME?
- I'M TERRIBLY SORRY,
BUT I CAN'T REVEAL
ANY OF THAT INFORMATION...
JUST YET.
BUT I CAN TELL YOU THIS MUCH
SINCE YOU'RE ASKING.
I'M HERE ON
SOMEBODY'S ORDERS.
- SOMEONE SENT YOU?
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
SOMEONE WHO IS EXTREMELY
CONCERNED WITH YOUR WELL BEING.
GOTTA BE ON MY WAY.
- HEY, PLEASE DON'T GO.
WAIT UP.
I NEVER FOUND OUT
WHO SENT HIM.
WHO COULD HE BE
WORKING FOR ANYWAY?
- Azaka:
PRINCESS AYEKA?
HOW COME YOU'RE
STAYING UP SO LATE?
- HAVING A HARD TIME
FALLING ASLEEP?
- AZAKA AND KAMIDAKE,
I HAVE JUST MET...
- WHO?
- OH, NEVER MIND.
I CAN'T TELL ANYBODY BECAUSE
I DON'T KNOW WHO I'M
TALKING ABOUT.
- Sakuya: HOW DID YOU DO
ON THE EXAM, TENCHI?
- Tenchi:
I'M SURE I DID ALL RIGHT.
- THAT'S GOOD.
I'M REALLY AFRAID
I BLEW IT.
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU LOOKED LIKE YOU WERE
DOING JUST FINE.
- WELL, I FOOLED YOU.
TENCHI, DID YOU FIND
STUDYING AT HOME
ANY EASIER FOR YOU?
- HUH? AT OKAYAMA--
- Both: DON'T YOU DARE
TALK TO TENCHI.  IT'S MY TURN!
- UH...
- IS ANYTHING WRONG?
- HUH?
- UH-HUH.
- ( chuckles )
- THAT LAUGH SOUNDS
WAY TOO PHONY.
YOU SHOULD LIGHTEN UP, BRO.
- DON'T BE GLUM.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW LUCKY YOU ARE
TO HAVE SUCH A CUTE
GIRLFRIEND?
- WHY DO YOU THINK I'M GLUM?
WHY ARE YOU SAYING THAT?
- I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
BECAUSE I BELIEVE
YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT
SOME GIRL BACK IN OKAYAMA.
AM I RIGHT?
- OH.
- WHAT?  NO WAY, MAN.
- COME ON, TENCHI.
FESS UP.
OR I'LL HAVE TO
GIVE YOU A MELVIN,
MY NEWEST WRESTLING HOLD.
- KNOCK IT OFF, GUYS.
QUIT EMBARRASSING ME.
- ( giggles )
YOU HAVE SO MUCH FUN
TEASING EACH OTHER.
YOU MUST BE
BEST FRIENDS.
- ( chuckles )
YEAH, WE ARE.
- WE GET ALONG SO WELL
BECAUSE WE'RE SO SIMILAR.
- I AM NOT LIKE THEM AT ALL.
- THAT'S IT!
THERE'S BEEN TOO MANY
CHANGES AROUND HERE.
- Both: HUH?
- ( meows )
- I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D NOTICED.
BUT YOU SEE THEY WERE ALL
OUT OF OUR REGULAR MISO PASTE,
SO I HAD TO BUY
A DIFFERENT KIND.  SORRY.
- THAT IS NOT WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT!
- OH.  IS IT THE SPINACH
THAT BOTHERS YOU?
THE ORGANIC VEGETABLE MART
WAS CLOSED TODAY
SO I HAD TO SHOP AT
A REGULAR MARKET.
THEIR PRODUCE
DIDN'T LOOK TOO FRESH,
BUT THAT'S NOT MY FAULT.
- IT'S NOT THE SPINACH.
- I KNOW.
IT'S THE PAN-FRIED POTATOES
BEING KIND OF DRIED UP.
I WAS READING
A COMIC BOOK,
AND THE NEXT THING
YOU KNOW, I SMELLED SMOKE.
I GUESS THEY GOT
A LITTLE BIT BURNED.
- I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT
THE LOUSY FOOD!
OUR HOME HAS BEEN
CHANGED TOO MUCH.
WAY TOO MUCH.
I MEAN IT, LOOK AROUND!
I'M TALKING ABOUT
OUR CURRENT SITUATION.
- THE PRINCESS SEEMS TO BE
TOO TIGHTLY WOUND TODAY.
- SOUNDS TO ME LIKE SHE
COULD USE SOME MUSCLE RELAXANT.
- ( meows )
- WHAT SITUATION
DO YOU MEAN?
- RYOKO IS MISSING,
AND WE DON'T HAVE A CLUE
TO WHERE SHE IS.
MIHOSHI AND KIYONE WERE CALLED
BACK TO THEIR 62nd PRECINCT.
AND WASHU HAS BEEN
SHUT UP IN THE LABORATORY.
SHE HASN'T COME OUT
FOR AGES.
NOW DO YOU SEE MY POINT?
OVERCOOKED SPINACH
AND BURNT PAN-FRIED POTATOES?
OH!  ISN'T ANYONE
PAYING ATTENTION?
TENCHI USED TO BE THE BOND
THAT KEPT US ALL TOGETHER,
BUT LATELY EVERYONE
HAS LEFT TO GO OFF
TO DO WHATEVER IT IS THEY DO.
SOMETHING AWFUL WILL HAPPEN
UNLESS WE ALL GET
TOGETHER AGAIN.
AS YOU KNOW,
I'M THE JURAI CROWN PRINCESS.
I HAVE THE POWER
TO SENSE THAT DANGER
IS LOOMING OUT THERE.
- I THINK AYEKA'S
BEING PARANOID.
- ( meows )
- ( chuckles )
- OH...
( clears throat )
I NEED TO BRING
EVERYONE BACK,
BUT I'M NOT SURE
HOW TO BEGIN.
I CAN'T REACH RYOKO.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE SHE WENT.
AND MIHOSHI AND KIYONE'S
PRECINCT IS NEAR PLUTO,
WHICH IS FAR AWAY.
I CAN'T EXACTLY GO
KNOCKING ON THEIR DOOR.
( gasps )
WASHU, OPEN UP!
WASHU,
OPEN THIS DOOR AT ONCE!
LOOKS LIKE I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO FIND ANOTHER WAY.
HAND ME A MALLET NOW,
AZAKA.
- YES, PRINCESS.
- ( shouts )
( grunting )
A BIGGER MALLET.
- YES, PRINCESS.
- ( strains )
AAH!
( grunts )
HAND ME A SAW.
- YES, PRINCESS.
- THE DRILL MONSTER!
- AAH!
THERE IS ONLY ONE WAY LEFT.
I KNOW IT IS DANGEROUS,
BUT SHE LEAVES ME NO CHOICE.
- OH, NO.
NOT THAT, PLEASE.
- WON'T YOU RECONSIDER,
PRINCESS?
- THAT IS AN ORDER.
- Both: YES, PRINCESS.
- ( gasps )
- All: THE JURAI SUPER SUPREME
TOTAL ANNIHILATION BEAM.
- ( explosion )
- UH...
- OHH.
- ( meows )
- ( groans )
WHY WON'T YOU COME OUT?
( coughs )
- ( chuckles )
- OH.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING HERE
THAT I HAVEN'T USED YET.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL NEVER GIVE UP.
I'M DETERMINED.
I WILL FIND A WAY TO BRING
EVERYONE BACK TOGETHER.
- ( snoring meows )
- HMM.
MY TRAVEL TICKET.
- ( floor creaks )
- HMM?
( meows )
- DID YOU HAVE
A NICE SLEEP, DEAR?
I HOPE SO,
'CAUSE YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT!
- ( meows )
( meows )
- ( laughs )
LET THEM SEND THE WHOLE
GALAXY POLICE FLEET.
THEY'LL BE NO MATCH FOR ME.
- THEY'RE COMING.
- ( chuckles )
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
HEY, YOU MADE MY DAY!
- AND YOU'VE MADE MINE.
- HUH?
- NICE TO SEE YOU STILL
HAVE THAT MAGIC.
YOU'RE MAGNIFICENT.
- STOP.
I MIGHT THINK YOU MEAN IT.
- BUT I DO, RYOKO.
- Gyan: BATTLE STATIONS.
- HUH?
- Gyan: ENEMY AT TEN O'CLOCK
ON A 30 DEGREE ELEVATION.
DETECTING MULTIPLE OBJECTS
COMING OUT OF WARP
AND FAST APPROACHING
OUR SECTOR.
- CHANGE COURSE.
LET'S GO GET THEM.
- ROGER THAT.
- THEY DON'T GET IT.
THEY JUST KEEP
COMING AT ME.
YOU WON'T EVER CATCH ME.
HAVEN'T YOU FIGURED
THAT OUT YET?
- ( chuckles )
HMM.
( chuckles )
- ( laughs )
- Sasami: RYO-OHKI?
RYO-OHKI?
I WONDER WHERE
SHE COULD HAVE GONE TO.
I WANTED HER TO GO
OFF TO THE VEGETABLE
MARKET WITH ME.
( sighs )
- ( meows )
- FULL SPEED, RYO-OHKI.
OUR DESTINATION IS
THE 62nd PRECINCT.
- ( meows )
- THIS MISSION IS URGENT.
WE MUST CONTACT EVERYONE NOW.
IF WE FAIL TO DO SO,
SOMETHING TERRIBLE MAY HAPPEN.
- ( meows )
- ( siren blares )
- THAT'S MIHOSHI
AND KIYONE'S PATROL SHIP.
WOW!  WE MUST BE
COSMICALLY CONNECTED.
NO MATTER HOW
FAR APART WE WERE,
THEY WERE ABLE TO
SENSE MY PRESENCE HERE.
- Both: YES, PRINCESS.
- Kiyone: STOP RIGHT NOW
AND PULL THAT SHIP OVER.
I DON'T KNOW WHO
YOU CLOWNS ARE,
BUT YOU'RE EXCEEDING
THE SPEED LIMIT!
- All: WHAT?!
- WHAT IS THAT THING
YOU'RE WRITING?
- THIS WOULD BE
CALLED A TICKET.
- HUH?!
- EVEN THE JURAI PRINCESS
HAS TO OBEY THE TRAFFIC LAWS...
...NO EXCEPTIONS.
- HOW ARE YOU, HUH?
I'M JUST DELIGHTED TO SEE YOU,
PRINCESS, OH BOY!
- YOU WERE GOING 1,000 MILES
OVER THE LIMIT.
YOU MUST SIGN THIS FORM.
- OH...
HERE YOU GO.
- THIS COPY'S FOR YOU.
YOU CAN PAY YOUR TICKET
AT THE PRECINCT STATION,
OR SEND IT IN VIA THE GALAXY
FEDERATION POST OFFICE.
- OFFICER KIYONE?
OH!
- AND SEE TO IT
THAT THIS DOESN'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
- UH, KIYONE, WAIT.
I CAME ALL THIS WAY
TO TALK TO BOTH OF YOU.
- HUH?
- DON'T WALK AWAY.
I NEED TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
PLEASE LISTEN.
COME BACK WITH ME
TO OKAYAMA.
- OH!  WOW,
THAT WOULD BE WONDERFUL.
- AH.
- I MUST CONFESS TO YOU,
I MISS MY FAVORITE TV SHOW,
"SPACE POLICE POLICE MAN."
- All: THAT'S US!
- POLICE MAN?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO,
KIYONE?
- AS YOU KNOW,
OUR NEW APPOINTMENT
WAS OFFICIALLY
PASSED ONTO US
FROM GALAXY POLICE
HEADQUARTERS.
WE ARE NOT PERMITTED
TO CHANGE OUR BEAT ASSIGNMENTS
FOR PERSONAL REASONS.
- I HAVE AN IDEA.
I THINK IT JUST MIGHT WORK.
I WILL ASK
THE JURAI AUTHORITIES
TO CONTACT THE GALAXY POLICE
TO CHANGE YOUR APPOINTMENT.
- YEAH.  THEN WE'LL BE
BACK ON EARTH IN NO TIME FLAT.
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
I DON'T WANT AYEKA TO DO
ANY SUCH THING!
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
- WHY ARE YOU MAD?
I'M CONFUSED.
- WE FINALLY GET TRANSFERRED
FROM THE SUBSTATION
ON THAT REMOTE PLANET,
NOW YOU WANT TO GO BACK
AND EXPERIENCE MORE MISERY.
WELL, NOT ME.
- FOR HEAVEN'S SAKE,
DON'T TALK LIKE THAT,
KIYONE.
RYOKO IS MISSING,
WASHU HAS LOCKED HERSELF
UP IN HER LAB
AND WON'T COME OUT,
AND YOU'VE BEEN
REASSIGNED.
THIS IS ALL MAKING ME
TERRIBLY UPSET.
AND BESIDES,
I HAVE A PREMONITION
THAT THESE THINGS
ARE A BAD OMEN.
- OH, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT RYOKO.
WE KNOW WHERE TO FIND HER.
- WELL, WHERE IS SHE?
HUH?
- LOOK HERE.
- ARREST WARRANT?
- HER RAP SHEET
FOR THIS WEEK.
SHE ROBBED A GALAXY UNION BANK
14 TIMES,
THERE'S 157 DAMAGE REPORTS,
AND SHE SHOT DOWN 368 SHIPS
OF THE GALAXY POLICE FLEET.
SHE IS DESTROYING EVERYTHING
THAT COMES WITHIN HER RANGE.
SHE'S NOW BEEN UPGRADED
TO AN ULTRA CLASS-A CRIMINAL.
- IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
- WHAT'S NOT TO BELIEVE?
I MEAN, RYOKO'S A PROFESSIONAL
SPACE PIRATE.
- SHE'S GONE RIGHT BACK
TO HER OLD TRICKS.
IF YOU ASK ME,
WHEN SHE WAS ON EARTH,
SHE WAS LIKE
A FISH OUT OF WATER.
IF YOU HAPPEN TO SPOT HER,
DON'T SAY ANYTHING
TO TIP HER OFF. JUST REPORT
HER TO ME IMMEDIATELY.
- WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO WITH HER?
- WELL NOW,
WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE?
AFTER ALL, I AM A COP.
I'LL ARREST HER!
AND THEN BE ON MY WAY.
EVERYONE WILL CHEER
MY TRIUMPHANT CAPTURE,
AND I'LL BE PROMOTED
WITH TOP HONORS!
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU CAN'T TURN RYOKO IN,
YOU'D BE RATTING ON
YOUR OWN FRIEND.
- HOW CAN YOU EVEN IMAGINE
THAT RYOKO AND I ARE FRIENDS?
- COME ON.
WE ALL ATE TOGETHER,
WE PLAYED GAMES TOGETHER,
AND WE SHARED
THE JACUZZI TUB WITH
RYOKO, REMEMBER?
- STOP!  DON'T EVER
REPEAT THAT DRIVEL!
NO ONE AT POLICE HEADQUARTERS
CAN HEAR A WORD ABOUT IT.
IF THEY DO, MY DREAMS
OF A PROMOTION
WILL GO UP IN SMOKE.
IT NEVER HAPPENED.
PLEASE DON'T.
( whimpers )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HUH?
( clears throat )
THAT TIME I SPENT ON EARTH
IS ANCIENT HISTORY.
I'D RATHER NOT BE
REMINDED OF IT.
I WASN'T ENTIRELY MYSELF
WHILE I WAS THERE.
- IS THIS YOU?
- I GUESS IT IS FOR NOW.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT KIYONE'S CHANGED
QUITE A BIT.
- MIHOSHI,
LET'S GET GOING.
- HEY, THAT HURTS!
DON'T PULL SO HARD, KIYONE.
- QUIT COMPLAINING AND COME ON.
MOVE IT!
- ( laughs )
- Both: WHAT WILL WE
DO NOW, PRINCESS?
- AZAKA AND KAMIDAKE,
WE'RE GOING HOME.
- Both: YES, PRINCESS.
- ( meows )
- ( Sasami humming )
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- AYEKA, THE BATH IS READY
IF YOU WANT TO JUMP IN.
- ( meows )
- I HAVE TO GET UP
VERY EARLY TOMORROW,
SO I'LL BE GOING
TO BED NOW.
- ( meows )
- 'NIGHT.
- AYEKA SEEMS DEPRESSED.
I WISH WE COULD HELP HER.
- ( meows )
- ( sighs )
HMM?
-  ( beeps )
- ( phone rings )
- HUH?
HI, THIS IS TENCHI.
- Ayeka:
NICE TO HEAR YOUR VOICE.
- THAT YOU, PRINCESS?
- YES, IT'S ME.
I JUST CALLED TO ASK
IF YOU WOULD MIND
COMING HOME RIGHT NOW.
- WHY?  WHAT HAPPENED?
IS SOMETHING GOING ON THERE,
AYEKA?  TELL ME.
- WELL, NOT EXACTLY.
IT'S JUST THAT I HAVE
A GLOOMY PREMONITION
THAT SOMETHING HORRIBLE
MAY HAPPEN.
- Tenchi: LIKE WHAT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I'M PICKING UP
BAD VIBES
STARTING WITH OUR
FAMILY BREAKING UP.
WASHU HAS LOCKED HERSELF
UP IN THE LAB
AND HASN'T COME OUT
FOR SO LONG.
- THAT'S ALL?
DON'T WORRY.
SOUNDS PRETTY NORMAL TO ME.
- WELL, MIHOSHI
AND KIYONE ARE GONE.
THEY WERE TRANSFERRED TO
THE 62nd PRECINCT.
- THAT'S GREAT.
SOUNDS LIKE
A BIG STEP UP FOR THEM.
I BET THEY'RE VERY HAPPY.
- AND I STILL HAVEN'T
FOUND RYOKO
WHO LEFT HERE AS WELL.
- HUH?
WHAT ELSE IS NEW?
SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN
A VERY UNPREDICTABLE WOMAN.
DON'T BE UPSET.
SHE'LL TURN UP
ONE OF THESE DAYS,
I'M SURE OF IT.
- BUT DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S PRETTY ODD.
I MEAN, ALL OF US
WERE SO CLOSE
AND THEN WITHOUT ANY DISCUSSION
OR REAL REASON THAT I CAN SEE,
WE'VE ALL JUST
SUDDENLY SPLIT UP.
- YEAH, SO?
- IT HAPPENED SO FAST.
ALMOST LIKE THERE WAS
A FORCE BEHIND THESE EVENTS.
I GUESS THAT MUST SOUND
A LITTLE CRAZY TO YOU.
- AYEKA, YOU'RE BEING
A WORRYWART. QUIT IT.
THEY'LL ALL COME BACK
EVENTUALLY.
CHILL, OKAY?
I HAVE TO STUDY
FOR MY FINALS.
UNLESS THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE,
I'D BETTER GET BACK TO WORK.
SO GOOD-BYE NOW.
- WAIT!
PLEASE DON'T HANG UP ON ME,
TENCHI!
- HUH?
- TENCHI!
- YEAH?
- OH, GOOD.
YOU'RE THERE.
- WHAT'S WRONG, AYEKA?
- I-- I MEAN...
- WHAT IS IT?
- I JUST WANTED TO SAY...
THAT I...
I...
- ( kettle whistling )
- Tenchi: YEAH?
AYEKA?
- ( kettle whistles )
- I LOVE YOU, TENCHI.
VERY MUCH.
WORDS JUST CAN'T EXPRESS
MY FEELINGS FOR YOU.
- HUH?
- I LOVE YOU FROM
THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
TENCHI, I JUST WANTED YOU
TO KNOW THAT.
YOU MAY LAUGH,
BUT I CAN'T HELP IT.
I WORRY THAT IF WE'RE NOT
ALL AROUND TO TAKE CARE OF YOU,
SOMETHING JUST MIGHT
HAPPEN TO YOU.
SORRY TO BOTHER YOU.
IT'S DUMB.
BUT I HAD TO TELL YOU
I LOVE YOU
EVEN IF YOU'VE
HEARD IT BEFORE.
I JUST WANTED YOU
TO HEAR IT AGAIN.
- ( kettle whistles )
- TENCHI, ARE YOU LISTENING?
- YES, THAT WAS
SWEET OF YOU.
AND YOU KNOW I LIKE YOU
A LOT TOO.
- ( gasps )
I'M GLAD, TENCHI.
- ( doorbell rings )
- AYEKA, CAN YOU
HOLD ON A MINUTE?
SOMEBODY RANG MY DOORBELL.
HELLO, DON'T GO AWAY.
I'M ON THE PHONE.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
- BYE FOR NOW, TENCHI.
- ( chuckles )
- GOOD-BYE.
- HEY, WAIT.
WANNA COME IN
FOR SOME TEA?
- NO, I'D BETTER NOT.
I JUST WANTED TO BRING YOU
A MIDNIGHT SNACK.
- ALL RIGHT.
APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU.
- GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR STUDYING.
BYE-BYE.
- YOU TOO.
( chuckles )
OH.
THANKS FOR HOLDING.
NOW I'M BACK.
HUH?
- I JUST WON'T GIVE UP.
I'LL FIND SOME WAY
TO BRING US BACK TOGETHER.
AND I WILL HAVE TENCHI
BACK WITH ME.
I CAN DO IT, AYEKA.
I CAN DO IT.
- SHE'S NOT ALL THAT SMART,
IS SHE?
SHE'S UNAWARE THAT
WHEN SHE TRIES
TO BRING THEM TOGETHER,
THEY GET FURTHER APART.
- IT SHOULDN'T BE SURPRISING,
I EXPECT.
EVERYONE'S FATE IS DIFFERENT.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meows )
( meows )
- Kiyone:
HI, I'M KIYONE.
IT WAS ONLY A SHORT WHILE AGO
WE ALL LIVED AS ONE
BIG HAPPY FAMILY ON EARTH.
WHO COULD HAVE IMAGINED THEN
THAT THERE WOULD COME A DAY
WHEN WE WOULD HAVE TO
ARREST RYOKO!
BUT DUTY IS DUTY,
AND WHEN I ACCOMPLISH
THIS MISSION SUCCESSFULLY,
MY RETURN TO HQ
AND MY PROMOTION
ARE GUARANTEED.
LET'S GO, MIHOSHI.
WE'LL ARREST
THE SPACE PIRATE RYOKO
ALL BY OURSELVES.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF
THE NEW TENCHI MUYO SERIES,
"OLD FRIENDS."