- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- MAY YOU BE FILLED
WITH PEACE AND PURE SPIRIT.
- Dokuzen:
WELL, WELL, WELL.
IT ALMOST APPEARS AS IF
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
- OH, MASTER?
- YOU KNOW,
SOME OF IT
LOOKS PRETTY GOOD.
BUT YOUR FORM ISN'T
QUITE RIGHT YET.
YOU MUST SWING
THE SACRED STAFF SMOOTHLY.
WATCH ME.
( groans )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( groans )
- ( pants )
- YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE PUSHED
YOUR BODY SO HARD.
- Sakuya: HOLD IT,
DON'T MOVE.
JUST STAY RIGHT THERE
AND SMILE.
- CHEESE!
- ( groans )
- YOU MOVED!
I SAID DON'T.
- SAKUYA,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- GEE, ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I'M TAKING YOUR PICTURE.
- WHY?
- ( laughs )
- I WANT TO MAKE
A VISUAL RECORD
OF MY SUMMER BREAK WITH YOU
TO PUT IN MY PHOTO ALBUM
TO REMEMBER
OUR TIME TOGETHER.
- SAKUYA.
- I PLAN TO BE TAKING
PICTURES AROUND HERE
UNTIL YOUR TRAINING IS OVER.
YOU'LL GET USED TO IT.
- OH.
- HMPH.
- SO DON'T MIND ME, OKAY?
JUST GO ON AND DO
WHATEVER YOU NORMALLY DO.
- ( camera clicks )
( clicking )
- IT SEEMS A BIT STRANGE.
WHAT SHE DOES
MAKES NO SENSE TO ME.
- OH, SMILE.
- Ayeka:
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?!
I CAN'T BELIEVE MY EARS!
SASAMI, TELL ME AGAIN
WHAT YOU SAID.
- YESTERDAY,
RIGHT BEFORE MY EYES,
MY FRIEND YUGI
SUDDENLY DISAPPEARED.
- ( wind whooshes )
- ( explosion )
- ( thinking ) SHE SAID
THAT HIDEOUS NAME AGAIN.
HOW MANY YUGIS
CAN THERE BE?
- HUH?
WHAT'S THE MATTER, AYEKA?
CAT GOT YOUR TONGUE?
- ( meows )
- THAT EVIL BEING WHO
ATTACKED THE MASAKI SHRINE
CALLED HERSELF YUGI ALSO.
- WHAT?! IT'S GOT TO BE
JUST A COINCIDENCE.
- ALL RIGHT, SASAMI,
LET'S FIND OUT
IF IT'S COINCIDENCE,
ALL RIGHT?
WAIT THERE.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I'M PRETTY SURE THIS ONE
CAPTURES HER APPEARANCE.
- DO YOU THINK I GOT
HER EYES RIGHT, RYO-OHKI?
- ( meows )
- I'M DONE WITH MINE.
NOW, SASAMI, TELL ME.
IS THIS YOUR FRIEND?
- NO, THIS IS MY YUGI.
I'M NOT SURE
ABOUT THAT ONE.
OUR DRAWINGS
DON'T LOOK ALIKE.
- HMPH.
THIS IS A BUST.
THERE MUST BE A BETTER WAY
TO SHOW YOU HER.  AH!
- ( computer beeps )
- WHAT'S UP?
YOU NEED MY HELP?
- MISS WASHU,
COULD YOU PLEASE
SHOW SASAMI THE VIDEO TAPE
YOU MADE OF YUGI?
- NO PROBLEM.
HERE YOU GO.
( snaps )
- NOW REMEMBER SHE ATTACKED
THE MASAKI SHRINE.
EXAMINE HER FACE CAREFULLY.
- ( silent )
( laughs )
- ( gasps )
- ( Yugi laughs )
SASAMI.
- Sasami: YUGI!
- ( laughs )
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THERE MUST BE SOME
KIND OF MISTAKE.
- Yugi: SASAMI.
( laughs )
- Kid: YEAH, I'LL SEE YOU
OVER BY THE TREE.
- ( groans )
- YEAH, PERFECT.
THE LIGHT'S JUST RIGHT.
- ( slurps )
- NOW DON'T BE SO STIFF,
TENCHI.
LOOSEN UP.
I WANT A PICTURE
OF YOU HAVING FUN.
- YOU'RE MAKING ME FEEL
SELF-CONSCIOUS.
HOW CAN I HAVE FUN?
- OH, STOP WHINING.
- ( laughs )
- I WANT YOU TO SPEND
THE WHOLE DAY WITH ME
UNTIL I GET
THE PERFECT PICTURE.
- YUP, GREAT.  OH.
THAT'S A REALLY
NICE CAMERA.
IS IT YOUR FATHER'S?
- NO, IT'S MINE.
WHY DO YOU ASK?
- OH, YOU NEVER
TALK ABOUT IT,
BUT YOU MUST COME FROM
A PRETTY WEALTHY FAMILY.
- HUH?
WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
- WELL, BECAUSE THAT
CAMERA YOU'VE GOT
IS ONE OF THOSE
VERY EXPENSIVE KINDS.
- I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
HUH.
- WHAT PROFESSIONS EXACTLY
DO YOUR MOM AND DAD
MAKE A LIVING IN?
IF YOU DON'T MIND MY ASKING.
- WHY DO YOU WANT
TO KNOW THAT?
- WELL, WHY NOT?
COME TO THINK OF IT,
YOU NEVER TALK ABOUT THEM.
- ( laughs )
- HUH?
- OH, I GET IT.
YOU WANT TO GO MEET MY PARENTS.
AM I RIGHT?
- HUH?!
NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT,
REALLY.
I WAS JUST CURIOUS.
- FORGET ABOUT THEM.
LET'S GO TAKE SOME MORE
PICTURES IN THE PARK
BEFORE IT GETS TOO DARK.
- HUH?  HEY, WAIT FOR ME.
I'M COMING.
OWW!
- ( clattering )
- ( gasps )
AH, SMILE.
- ( groans )
- HUH?
I DON'T GET IT.
CAN SOMEBODY EXPLAIN?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( grunts )
YUGI'S STORY BEGAN
3500 YEARS AGO.
- Both: SINGLE-HANDEDLY,
SHE ALMOST SUCCEEDED
IN DESTROYING
THE JURAI PLANET.
- AND NOW SHE'S BACK,
THIS TIME ATTACKING
THE MASAKI FAMILY SHRINE.
WHAT'S WORSE, SHE'S PRETENDING
TO BE YOUR FRIEND.
AND I DIDN'T KNOW!
- THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
IT MUST BE A DIFFERENT PERSON.
YUGI WOULDN'T HARM ME
OR ANYBODY.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
SHE'S MY FRIEND.
SHE ONLY WANTS ME
TO BE HER FRIEND.
- SHE'S BEEN LYING TO YOU.
INNOCENTLY, YOU BOUGHT
INTO HER BIG, FAT LIE.
- IT'S NOT TRUE.
- ( meows )
( whimpers )
- RYO-OHKI!
- ( meowing )
- ( clangs )
- ( pitiful meows )
- RYO-OHKI!
- OUR TRAPS
ARE WORKING PERFECTLY.
- ( laughs )
- FROM OUR POINT OF VIEW,
YOU'VE OVERDONE IT.
- NOW, LOOK, I'M DOING MY BEST
WITHOUT MIHOSHI,
KIYONE, AND TENCHI.
AND ALTHOUGH IT DOESN'T
REALLY MATTER MUCH,
RYOKO IS NOT
HERE TO HELP EITHER.
I ALONE MUST PROTECT
THE MASAKI FAMILY.
- THE PRINCESS IS RIGHT.
- OF COURSE, WE'LL DO
ANYTHING WE CAN TO HELP.
YOU CAN COUNT ON US.
- MM-HMM, MM-HMM.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
WE HAVE WORK TO DO.
WE NEED TO TEST
ANOTHER TRAP TO SEE
IF IT WILL BE STRONG ENOUGH
TO PROTECT THE WHOLE HOUSE.
- ( all groaning )
- ( clattering )
- ( groaning )
- DO YOU THINK
MY FRIEND YUGI
IS CAPABLE OF DOING
THE HORRIBLE THINGS
AYEKA CLAIMS SHE DID?
- Both: PRINCESS AYEKA,
CAN YOU HEAR US?
- Sakuya: TENCHI,
MOVE TO THE RIGHT.
YOU'RE OUT OF THE LIGHT.
- UH-HUH.
MY RIGHT?  YOUR RIGHT?
WHICH RIGHT?
- YOUR RIGHT.
TAKE A STEP BACK.
NOW DON'T MOVE.
- ( camera clicks )
- SORRY,
BUT I WASN'T SMILING
AND I THINK I BLINKED.
- ( laughs ) RIGHT, I BETTER
TAKE ANOTHER PICTURE.
- ( clicks )
- WHY DON'T I TAKE
YOUR PICTURE THIS TIME?
- I'D RATHER SEE
IF WE CAN GET
SOMEBODY TO TAKE A PICTURE
OF US TOGETHER.
- ( thinking )
SOONER OR LATER,
THOSE GUYS GOT
TO TAKE A BREAK
AND THEN I MAKE MY MOVE.
- WHAT'S HE DOING?
- NOT MUCH OF ANYTHING.
- Sakuya: EXCUSE ME, GENTLEMEN.
- ( gasps )
- I NEED A FAVOR.
WILL YOU TAKE OUR PHOTO?
- Both: WHY SURE, MISS.
HAPPY TO BE OF SERVICE.
- OKAY, YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD.
- COULD YOU PLEASE
WAIT JUST A MOMENT?
- HUH?
OH!
- MUCH BETTER.
( giggles )
- ( chuckles )
- READY FOR YOUR MUG SHOT.
- ( clicking )
- Both:
THANKS A LOT, FELLAS.
- HEY, COME GET ME.
- Both: HUH?
- ( laughs )
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE.
- Both: HUH?
- YOU'VE BEEN TAKING
A LOT OF SHOTS.
I WAS WONDERING
WHY YOU GOT
THIS SUDDEN INTEREST
IN PHOTOGRAPHY.
- AH, HMM.
I DON'T KNOW.
I SUPPOSE IT'S SOMETHING
I REALLY WANT TO DO.
- SAKUYA?
- YES.
- YOU'RE ORIGINALLY
FROM TOKYO, RIGHT?
- WHY DO YOU ASK?
- WELL, I JUST REALIZED
I DON'T REALLY KNOW
VERY MUCH ABOUT YOU.
LIKE, I WAS WONDERING,
DO YOU LIVE HERE IN TOKYO
WITH YOUR PARENTS?
- UH, I'M NOT SURE.
AH, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WHY DON'T WE GO
GET ICE CREAM?
- UH...
- COME ON, LET'S GO.
- OKAY.
- ( snickers ) THIS ISN'T
GONNA BE ALL THAT EASY.
( snickers )
- I MUST BE
SEEING THINGS.
I DON'T REMEMBER MY HOUSE
LOOKING LIKE THIS.
I GUESS THIS WILL TEACH ME
TO LEAVE WORK EARLY.
- THIS IS YOUR ONLY WARNING.
DO NOT TAKE ANOTHER STEP.
THIS HOUSE IS OFF-LIMITS
TO CIVILIAN PERSONNEL.
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
IT MUST BE SOME KIND OF JOKE.
HUH?
- ( explosion )
- ( screams )
- WELL, YOU CAN'T SAY I DIDN'T
TRY TO WARN YOU.
- Vendor: SO, SWEETIE,
IS THAT YOUNG MAN YOUR DATE?
- HUH?
YUP.
- AH, TO BE YOUNG LIKE YOU
IS WONDERFUL.
- I'LL BET YOU HAD
A LOT OF DATES YOURSELF
WHEN YOU WERE YOUNG.
- IT WAS DIFFERENT BACK THEN.
YOU HAD TO BE
CHAPERONED EVERYWHERE.
IF YOU LIKED A GIRL,
YOU COULD NEVER BE ALONE.
- THAT'S AWFUL.
- YOU JUST EARNED A FREE SCOOP.
- WOW.
- HAVE FUN.
- WE WILL.
THANK YOU, SIR.
- AH, BET THEY AREN'T
EXPECTING ME
TO USE THE BACK DOOR.
WATCH ME FOOL 'EM.
AAH!
AAHH!
- OPEN FIRE.
INTRUDER SPOTTED.
- ( explosions )
- ( screaming )
( groaning )
- Kamidake:
INTRUDER DOWN AND OUT.
- ( eating loudly )
HMM, EATING ICE CREAM
LIKE THIS IS NICE AND COOL.
- ( giggles )
REALLY?
I BETTER TRY IT.
OH!
( whimpers )
IT'S FREEZING.
- COME ON, LET'S GO.
- MY WHOLE BODY
IS KIND OF STIFF AND SORE.
- ( giggles )
I'M SORRY IF I WAS A BIT
TOO HARD ON YOU ALL DAY.
- YEAH, I BET.
PHOTO SESSIONS ALWAYS
TAKE A LOT OUT OF YOU.
- HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
- BECAUSE THAT'S
HOW IT'S BEEN
EVERY TIME I'VE HAD
A GROUP PHOTO TAKEN.
SOMEONE ALWAYS
CLOSES HIS EYES OR MOVES.
THEN THE SHOT
HAS TO BE DONE OVER
UNTIL, FINALLY,
EVERYONE LOOKS JUST RIGHT.
SAKUYA, HAVEN'T YOU EVER
TAKEN A GROUP PHOTO BEFORE?
- UM...
I DON'T KNOW.
- HOW CAN YOU NOT KNOW?
HAVEN'T YOU EVER
TAKEN PICTURES
WHEN YOU WENT ON FAMILY TRIPS
OR SCHOOL PICNICS?
SOMEBODY'S ALWAYS MAKING YOU
POSE FOR THE CAMERA.
- I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
- WELL, LOOK
IN YOUR PHOTO ALBUM.
YOU MUST HAVE AT LEAST
ONE GROUP PICTURE,
MAYBE A PHOTO
OF YOUR FAMILY TOGETHER.
- MAYBE.
BUT I CAN'T REMEMBER...
MY HOUSE, MY FAMILY,
NONE OF IT.
I DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY DON'T.
- SAKUYA?
- ( meows )
- Minion: DON'T EVEN
THINK ABOUT MOVING.
- HEY, LOOK WHAT I FOUND.
- ( gasps )
PLEASE DON'T TAKE
THE VILLAGE TREASURE.
STOP.
( grunting )
( whimpers )
- HEY, TAKE IT EASY.
I'LL MAKE GOOD USE OF
YOUR TOWN'S TREASURE,
OLD-TIMER, DON'T YOU
WORRY ABOUT THAT.
- WHAT ARE YOU INTENDING
TO DO WITH IT.
- HMM, I CAN SELL IT
FOR A HANDSOME PRICE
ON THE BLACK MARKET.
- NO, I BEG YOU.
- I MIGHT DONATE IT
FOR TARGET PRACTICE
IN A SPACE SHOOTING CONTEST.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
I COULD USE IT AS AN ANCHOR
FOR MY SPACESHIP.
( cackles )
- Boy: STOP IT!
- ( growls )
- YOU SCUMMY SPACE PIRATE,
YOU CAN'T HAVE OUR
VILLAGE TREASURE.
I WON'T LET YOU.
NOW YOU BETTER GIVE IT BACK
OR GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE I BEAT YOU UP--
( grunts )
- ( gasping )
- YOU'RE A BRAZEN, GUTSY KID.
- COVER YOUR EYES, HONEY.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO WATCH.
- I DON'T LIKE SNIVELING.
KNOCK IT OFF.
YOUR LITTLE BRAT'S
NOT GONNA GET HURT.
- HUH?
DON'T CALL ME A LITTLE BRAT!
- ( growls )
JUST BACK OFF!
I WAS GONNA LET YOU LIVE!
BUT NOT ANYMORE.
NIGHTY-NIGHT.
- ( screams )
- Woman: OH NO!
- ( whimpering )
- DON'T STOP, RYOKO.
- ( strains )
- ( whimpers )
- RYOKO.
- MM-HMM.
- ( grunts )
- TENCHI.
- ( sirens wail )
- Kiyone: WE MISSED
RYOKO ONCE AGAIN.
WE'RE ALWAYS JUST
ONE STEP BEHIND HER, OH BOY.
- Mihoshi: WATCH OUT. THE
ENEMY'S COMING UP FROM BEHIND.
- ROTATING ALL GUN POSITIONS
TO THE REAR!
( growls )
- ( sighs )
- THE ENEMY'S SNEAKED UP ON HIM.
HE'S GOT HIM.
WHAT A COWARD YOU ARE,
DRILL WORM BAZOOKA MAN.
- UGH!
- HOW DO YOU LIKE
THEM APPLES, COPPER?
HAHA, THE WHOLE UNIVERSE
IS MINE NOW.
- NOT SO FAST.
SEE, NOBODY OWNS OUTER SPACE,
NOT EVEN YOU, DRILL WORM
BAZOOKA MAN, YOU MADMAN.
YOU WON'T WIN!
( grunts )
HMM, HA HA HA,
YOU CAN'T KILL ME.
I'M THE MEANEST BAD MAN
IN OUTER SPACE.
( exaggerated groan )
THIS TIME
YOU'VE GOT ME GOOD.
- IS YOUR LITTLE
UNIVERSE SAFE AGAIN?
- WHA--
- 'CAUSE THIS UNIVERSE
COULD USE SOME HELP
IF YOU'RE NOT TOO BUSY.
- OH, PLEASE
DON'T BE MAD AT ME.
I WAS BORED AND I MISS
MY FAVORITE TV SHOW
"SPACE POLICE POLICEMAN."
- YOU SURE LOOK LIKE YOU
WERE HAVING A GREAT TIME.
AMAZING, WHAT'D YOU DO?
BUY OUT AN ENTIRE TOY STORE
SO YOU COULD
FILL UP THE COCKPIT
WITH ALL YOUR
"SPACE COP" THINGS?
I'M GONNA THROW
THIS STUFF INTO SPACE.
( gasps )
- PLEASE DON'T THROW AWAY
MY "SPACE POLICE" POLICEMEN.
I WON'T PLAY WITH MY TOYS
MORE THAN THREE TIMES A DAY,
I PROMISE.
- ( sighs )
- OR MAYBE TWICE A DAY.
ONCE A DAY WILL BE FINE,
OKAY?
PLEASE, KIYONE.
- HMPH, HOW ABOUT WE VISIT
EARTH ON OUR NEXT VACATION?
- WHAT?
YIPPEE!  OH, YAY!
LET'S DO IT.
I'LL GET TO WATCH
MY FAVORITE TV SHOW
AND GET TAPES OF THE ONES
I MISSED FROM SASAMI.
SHE'S BEEN RECORDING
THEM ALL FOR ME.
- ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE TO GET THE CHIEF'S
APPROVAL FIRST, THOUGH.
- WE SHOULD START PLACING
OUR VACATION REQUESTS NOW.
- ( giggles )
MAYBE I'LL CHECK OUT YOUR SHOW.
I MIGHT ENJOY IT.
- WE'LL WATCH IT TOGETHER.
"SPACE POLICE POLICEMAN"
IS GREAT.
YOU'LL LIKE IT.
( giggles )
- ( Sakuya laughs )
- ( Tenchi laughs )
- BETTER CHECK
THIS ONE OUT.
YOU'RE MOUTHLESS.
- THIS IS A REAL CHARMER TOO.
- OH!
( gasps )
WHAT A HORRIBLE PICTURE.
AH, I'D BETTER BURN
THE NEGATIVE.
OH!
- ( laughs )
( continues laughing )
IS ORANGE JUICE
ALL RIGHT, SAKUYA?
- SURE.
TENCHI?
- HMM?
- WOULD YOU LIKE
TO PUT THIS ON YOUR DESK?
- YUP, THANKS A LOT.
- WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
- NOT MUCH OF ANYTHING REALLY.
- OH, HUH.
YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT
THINKING ABOUT
WHAT THE GIRL FROM OKAYAMA
SAID YESTERDAY?
- NO, CERTAINLY NOT.
- I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
- WHAT?
- YOU WANT TO RUSH BACK
TO OKAYAMA RIGHT AWAY.
DON'T DENY IT!
IT'S TRUE.
BUT YOU PROMISED ME
THAT WE WERE
GOING TO SPEND THIS SUMMER
WITH EACH OTHER.
- ( sighs )
- BESIDES,
THERE'S NOTHING
YOU CAN DO
EVEN IF YOU DID GO BACK
TO OKAYAMA.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- EVERYONE IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THEIR OWN LIVES,
MAKING THEIR OWN DECISIONS.
NOBODY CAN DICTATE
TO RYOKO OR AYEKA
HOW THEY MUST
LIVE THEIR LIVES.
AM I RIGHT?
- YOU PROBABLY ARE,
BUT I WASN'T GOING FOR THEM.
- OKAYAMA'S MY HOMETOWN.
I JUST FEEL LIKE GOING HOME.
WELL, DON'T YOU SOMETIMES
THINK ABOUT GOING HOME, SAKUYA?
- I ONLY THINK ABOUT TOKYO.
ALL I KNOW IS HERE.
- Tenchi: ( echoes ) DO YOU LIVE
HERE IN TOKYO WITH YOUR PARENTS?
( echoes )
WHAT ARE THEIR PROFESSIONS?
YOU NEVER TALK ABOUT THEM.
( echoes ) CAN'T YOU LOOK
IN YOUR PHOTO ALBUM?
( echoes ) DON'T YOU HAVE
PHOTOS OF YOUR FAMILY?
- ( gasps )
- HOW CAN YOU NOT KNOW?
( echoes ) TELL ME.
- ( gasping )
( whimpering )
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING...
ABOUT MY FAMILY.
NO MEMORY OF ANY KIND.
ALL I KNOW IS TENCHI.
- HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH!
SAKUYA!  SAKUYA!
WAKE UP.
- ( gasps )
YES, TENCHI, WHAT IS IT?
- OH, GOOD, YOU'RE BACK.
SAKUYA,
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- KEEP YOUR EYES ON ME.
- HUH?
- PLEASE LISTEN.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
BE HERE FOR ME
AND ME ONLY.
DON'T LOOK
AT ANYBODY ELSE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
- ( gasps )
TENCHI...
I-- I AM--
( cries )
- WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
- ( door opens )
( door closes )
- HA, EVEN THEY
WOULDN'T EXPECT
ANYBODY TO COME
THROUGH THIS LAKE.
HMM, I WONDER WHAT THIS IS.
- ( rattles )
- THIEF ALERT!
SECURITY IS READY.
- ( screams )
- ( explosion )
- ( screaming )
- SOUNDS LIKE ANOTHER SCOUNDREL
JUST GOT TRAPPED.
THAT'S OUR THIRD ONE.
- HMM.
- ( meows )
- ( thinking )
YUGI, THEY SAY
YOU ATTACKED
THE MASAKI SHRINE.
YOU DIDN'T DO THAT,
DID YOU?
YOU MEANT IT WHEN YOU SAID
YOU WERE FRIENDS, RIGHT?
I KNOW YOU DID.
- ( thinking ) SASAMI,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE MY FRIEND.
YOU SHOULD MOVE TO MY PLACE.
WE CAN LIVE THERE TOGETHER.
- WHAT?
- IT'LL BE THE MOST
PERFECT FRIENDSHIP.
I JUST CAN'T WAIT.
- I'M SORRY, BUT
THAT'S A CRAZY IDEA.
WE CAN'T POSSIBLY
LIVE ON OUR OWN.
AFTER ALL, WE'RE STILL
JUST CHILDREN.
- ( echoes )
DON'T YOU DISAPPOINT ME!
SASAMI, I'M HERE
WAITING FOR YOU.
WON'T YOU PLEASE
COME TO ME?
BECAUSE IT'S TERRIBLE
TO BE ALL ALONE.
MY WORLD SHALL EMERGE.
THE TIME IS APPROACHING.
MATARI, TSUGARU!
- Tsugaru: YES, MA'AM.
- LET'S MAKE PREPARATIONS.
IT'S SHOWTIME.
( cackles )
( laughter continues )
- ( alarm rings )
- ( pulsing )
- Both: HUH?
( screams )
- ( Yugi laughing )
( laughter continues )
- ( sighs )
HMM.
- MY HOME, MY FAMILY,
MY MEMORY,
I DON'T HAVE ANY
OF THESE THINGS.
IF TENCHI CAN RECALL
THE HOMETOWN WHERE HE GREW UP
AND HIS FAMILY
THAT LIVES THERE,
THEN I SHOULD HAVE A MEMORY
OF MY OWN FAMILY
AND A HOME SOMEWHERE TOO.
BUT I JUST DON'T.
IT'S ALL BLANK.
I CAN'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING IN MY LIFE
BEFORE I MET TENCHI.
BUT HOW CAN THAT BE?
WHY CAN'T I REMEMBER?
( cries )
TENCHI, PLEASE HELP.
PLEASE HELP ME, TENCHI.
YOU'RE THE ONLY
ONE WHO CAN.
HELP ME.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meowing )
( meows )
- Ayeka:
AYEKA HERE.
RYOKO HAS GONE
TO OUTER SPACE
AND DOESN'T SEEM
TO BE COMING BACK.
KIYONE AND MIHOSHI
HAVE GONE TO PLUTO
AND THEY DON'T SEEM
TO BE COMING BACK.
AND LORD TENCHI HAS GONE
TO TOKYO
AND HE DOESN'T SEEM
TO BE COMING BACK EITHER.
TALK ABOUT BEING
LEFT BEHIND.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
I KNOW.
IT'S UP TO ME
TO KEEP OUR HOME SAFE
WHILE LORD TENCHI IS AWAY.
ALL RIGHT, NOW
I'M READY FOR ACTION.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF
THE NEW TENCHI MUYO SERIES...