- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yugi: SASAMI.
SASAMI!
- ( Yugi laughs )
- ( gasps )
- Sasami:
WHO-- WHO IS IT?
WHO'S CALLING ME?
IT'S YOU.
YUGI.  YUGI.
IT IS YOU, ISN'T IT?
- YOU REMEMBERED ME.
- OF COURSE.
I WOULD NEVER FORGET YOU.
- SASAMI, COME TO THE LAKE
IN THE HILLS
BEHIND YOUR HOUSE TOMORROW,
WHEN THE FULL MOON RISES
IN THE EASTERN SKY.
- LAKE IN THE HILLS
BEHIND THE HOUSE.
SURE, I'LL BE THERE.
CAN I BRING RYO-OHKI WITH ME?
- YES, BUT PLEASE BE SURE
TO COME.
PROMISE ME.
- Sasami: OH!
- WHAT WERE YOU
DREAMING OF, YUGI?
- I WENT TO SAY HELLO
TO MY FRIEND.
I TOLD HER THAT I'M COMING
TO SEE HER TOMORROW.
- AH, YOU'RE CLOSING IN.
- YES, THEIR FAMILY TIES
MAY BE STRONG, BUT IT'S ABOUT
TO COME APART AT THE SEAMS.
AND I WILL TEAR IT TO PIECES
WITH MY OWN HANDS.
( laughing )
- ( towel snaps )
- ( Sasami humming )
- ( meowing )
- HUH?  WHAT ARE YOU SAYING,
THAT YOU'RE IN A GOOD MOOD?
WELL, I SURE AM.
WANNA KNOW WHY?
- ( meowing )
- THEN I'LL TELL YOU.
LAST NIGHT I SAW A GOOD FRIEND.
SHE CAME TO ME IN A DREAM.
- ( meows )
- THE LAKE IN THE HILLS
BEHIND THE HOUSE.
- COME ON!
- ( grunting )
- ( shouting )
- SCORE!  WOW!
TENCHI'S STRONGER THAN HE LOOKS.
- ( panting )
- Boy #2: WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
HE'S ONE OF THOSE COUNTRY BOYS.
- Girl: COME ON, SAKUYA.
- ( all laughing )
- Girl #2: HEY, WAIT FOR ME!
- ( whistle blowing )
- COME ON, GUYS, HUH?
- HI. ( laughs )
I'M STARTING TO LIKE IT HERE.
GUESS DAD WAS RIGHT.
- WAVING TO THE GIRLS,
ARE YOU?
WELL, ISN'T THAT SWEET?
COME ON, COUNTRY BOY,
LET'S SEE HOW YOU HANDLE
MY DOUBLE HAMMER LOCK.
- Tenchi: GET YOUR FOOT OUT
OF MY MOUTH!
- HANG IN THERE, MY SON.
YOU ARE IN THE SPRINGTIME
OF YOUR LIFE.
YOU ONLY LIVE ONCE,
SO ENJOY YOUR YOUTH
WITH SOMEONE YOU LOVE
IN A PURE, UPRIGHT
AND BEAUTIFUL WAY.
THAT'S MY WISH,
AS YOUR FATHER.
AND THANK GOODNESS THAT GIRL
DOESN'T FLY
OR SHOOT LASER BEAMS OUT
OF HER HANDS,
LIKE YOUR OTHER GIRLFRIENDS.
- ( sighs )
MY MOVES ARE TOTALLY OFF LATELY,
AND IT'S BECAUSE TENCHI'S GONE.
I CAN SEE HIM ALL I WANT,
BUT IF I CAN'T BE WITH HIM,
WHAT'S THE USE?
LOVE MAKES A GIRL BEAUTIFUL.
FOR THE SAKE OF MY BEAUTY,
TENCHI, DO COME HOME TO ME.
( crying ) TENCHI.
WHO CARES?
I LAUGH AT HEARTACHE!
( laughs )
( sighs )
I WONDER WHAT HE'S DOING
RIGHT THIS MINUTE.  ( groans )
- Man: I SEE.
- ( gasps )
- SO HE IS THE ONE
WHO MAKES YOU SO RADIANT.
- WHO'S THERE?
- WELL, WELL.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- IT'S RYOKO.
AND WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- HOTSUMA.  I LIKE YOU.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
I CAN'T STAY.
COME BACK AGAIN AND WE WILL
SETTLE THIS ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- HOTSUMA!  YOU'RE BACK.
YOU REMEMBERED MY NAME.
I'M HONORED.
HOW UNEXPECTED OF YOU.
- GET OUT OF MY SIGHT,
DAMN YOU!
- OH, NO!
THAT MUST BE RYOKO AGAIN.
WELL, NEVER MIND.  LET'S GO.
- Ryoko:
YOU TRIED TO HURT TENCHI.
I NEVER FORGIVE ANYONE
FOR THAT.
- Hotsuma: VERY LOYAL OF YOU.
I DIDN'T COME HERE TO FIGHT YOU.
- WHO CARES WHAT YOU CAME FOR,
CREEP?
WHATEVER YOU ARE,
IT'S NOT CLOSE TO NORMAL.
- LOOK WHO'S TALKING,
RYOKO THE SPACE PIRATE.
- WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU ANYWAY?
- I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
I'M ONE OF YOUR OWN KIND, RYOKO.
I APOLOGIZE.
I PROMISE I'LL NEVER
HURT TENCHI AGAIN.
I WAS PLAYING A LITTLE GAME
WITH HIM ANYWAY,
AND I SUPPOSE I WAS
A BIT JEALOUS.
- JEALOUS?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I MEAN THAT
I WANT TO BE THE ONE
WHO MAKES YOU RADIANT.
- WHAT?
- I KNOW.  YOU'VE GOT A BIG
CRUSH ON ME, DON'T YOU?
MM-HMM.  MM-HMM.  I KNOW.
I KNOW.  IT'S SO TYPICAL.
TWO MEN FIGHT OVER THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL WOMAN ON EARTH.
OH, I AM SUCH A DIVA.
- HMM.
- WELL, SORRY,
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE A CHANCE.
FROM HEAD TO TOE, EVERY PART
OF ME BELONGS TO TENCHI.
THOUGH IF YOU'RE DESPERATE
FOR A GIRLFRIEND,
I COULD INTRODUCE YOU
TO AN UGLY GIRL CALLED AYEKA.
- GO HOME NOW.
- HUH?
- YOUR BELOVED TENCHI IS
IN DEEP TROUBLE.
- TROUBLE?
- THAT'S WHY I CAME HERE.
TO WARN YOU.
- HEY!
I DON'T LIKE IT AT ALL.
- ( wind howling )
- THE WIND IS HOWLING, AND THE
CLOUDS ARE SMEARED WITH BLOOD.
SOMETHING IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
- ( whimpering )
- THAT DOES IT, OLD MAN.
JUST WHAT KIND OF FATHER,
ARE YOU?
- HOW COULD YOU ALLOW TENCHI
TO GET TOGETHER WITH THAT WENCH?
- IT ISN'T FAIR.
YOU WENT ALL THE WAY THERE
TO SEE TENCHI AND YOU
DIDN'T EVEN TELL US.
- YOU TRICKED US, NOBUYUKI.
- HMM? ( laughs )
- ( screaming )
NO!  HELP ME!
- NO, I CAN'T STAND IT.
TENCHI IS THERE
WITH THAT MINX.
THEY COULD BE DOING ANYTHING,
JUST IMAGINE.
- NO, NOT TENCHI.  HE WOULDN'T.
- YEAH, DON'T BE SO SURE.
TENCHI IS A GUY
AND MEN GET IDEAS, YOU KNOW?
- IT CAN'T BE!  THEY'RE
TOGETHER!  THEY'RE A COUPLE!
( wailing )
- UGH!
- HUH?
- THE DIMENSIONAL TUNNEL
IS CLOSED.
- SORRY.
WE DON'T WANT ANY.
SO YOU CAN JUST STAY
ON YOUR OWN SIDE.
- GIVE ME SOME MONEY, OLD MAN.
I NEED IT TO BUY A TICKET
FOR THE BULLET TRAIN.
- BUILD ME A TIME MACHINE
AND MAKE IT SNAPPY.
- GIVE ME THE MONEY.
I'M SERIOUS NOW!
- I THINK I'M GONNA START
CRYING.  ( crying )
- DO YOU HAVE TO BE SO LOUD,
GIRLS?
- Ryoko: YOU THINK I'M KIDDING?
I'VE GOT TO GET TO
TENCHI TO STOP HIM!
- ( laughs )
- ( loud rumbling )
- ( grunts )
WHAT?!
- ( clamoring )
- Ayeka: WHAT WAS THAT?
- STOP!  GO BACK INSIDE!
- ( screeches )
- YUGI'S NOT COMING,
IS SHE?
WELL, IT WAS JUST A DREAM.
GUESS WE SHOULD GO.
ALL RIGHT.
( gasps )
- Ayeka:
WHATEVER ARE THOSE THINGS?
- Ryoko:
WHERE DID THEY COME FROM?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S BRIGHT AND GLOWING.
LOOK!
- YUGI, YOU'RE HERE.
- I'M SO GLAD YOU CAME,
SASAMI.
- ( meows )
- COME ON, TENCHI.
THIS WAY.  HURRY!
JUST WAIT.  YOU'VE GOT TO SEE
THIS GREAT LITTLE SHOP.
- OKAY, SLOW DOWN.
YOU'RE GONNA PULL MY ARM OFF.
- I AM YUGI,
THE NEW RULER
OF THIS LOWLY PLANET.
HEAR ME NOW, YOU MAGGOTS
OF THE MASAKI FAMILY.
FOR THE NOBLE AND SUPREME CAUSE,
SURRENDER YOUR LIVES TO ME.
- WELL, WHATEVER IT IS,
IT'S EVIL.
- WHAT DOES SHE MEAN?
- HEY, YUGI,
OR WHOEVER YOU ARE,
YOU NEED A LESSON IN MANNERS.
DIDN'T YOUR MOTHER EVER TEACH
YOU TO BE POLITE
TO BEAUTIFUL YOUNG LADIES
LIKE US?
- BEAUTY IS IN THE EYE
OF THE DESTROYER.
- ( screaming )
- ( sing-song )
GIRL IS GONNA GET MARRIED.
PUT A VEIL ON HER HEAD
NOT OXEN'S HORNS.
IF THE OXCART FALLS
WITH EVERYTHING IT CARRIES
ALL THE WEDDING THINGS
GET RUINED AND TORN
DON'T LET THE GROOM KNOW,
PUT OFF THE WEDDING
SO NOT EVEN THE SUN WILL KNOW--
- OH!
- ( wincing )
ARE YOU OKAY THERE, YUGI?
- I'M SORRY.
- ( laughs )
- ( meows )
- ( screaming )
- WHAT IS THAT LITTLE THING,
KIYONE?
IT'S SCARING ME.
- YOU DIDN'T STEAL A LOLLIPOP
FROM SOME KID WHO TURNED OUT
TO BE A DEMON, DID YOU?
- OF COURSE NOT.
I TOOK SOME KID'S ICE CREAM,
BUT THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
( screaming )
- LOOK OUT!  UGH!
- KAMIDAKE!
- DO NOT BE ALARMED, PRINCESS.
I WILL DO EVERYTHING
IN MY POWER TO KEEP YOU SAFE.
- THANK YOU.
- SHE'S GOT AMAZING
PSYCHIC STRENGTH.
LORD KATSUHITO.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO STOP IT.
EVEN IF WE COULD COMBINE
OUR POWERS,
I DON'T THINK
IT WILL BE ENOUGH.
IT'S TOO STRONG.
THIS COULD BE IT.
- DAMN IT.
- I SEE YOU WANNA PLAY
HIDE AND SEEK,
BUT I PREFER
LIGHTNING TAG.
- ( screaming )
- YOU THINK YOU CAN BEAT ME
WITH THOSE LITTLE TRICKS?
HA!  YOU MAKE ME LAUGH.
- A LADDER, TOKYO TOWER
AND HERE'S THE BRIDGE
OF SEPTORU.
YOU JUST GO LIKE THIS
AND THIS,
AND IT'S EASY.  SEE?
- ( grunting )
- YOU HAVE TO BRING THAT ONE TO
THIS SIDE LIKE THIS.  THAT'S IT.
- WHOA, IT WORKED!
- YOU GOT IT.  THAT'S GREAT.
THIS ONE'S FUN.
IT'S CALLED CAT'S CRADLE.
I LEARNED IT FROM GRANDPA.
I BET YOU CAN DO IT, TOO, YUGI.
- ARE YOU HAPPY, SASAMI?
- WHAT?
YEAH, I'M REALLY HAPPY.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE HERE,
AND IT'S SO FUN TO BE WITH YOU.
ARE YOU HAPPY, YUGI?
- I BELIEVE I AM.
- SAY, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO PICK SOME PRETTY FLOWERS?
- WHY?
- SO WE CAN MAKE A COLORFUL
FLOWER NECKLACE.
- OKAY.
- LET'S GO.  THIS WAY, YUGI.
- ( chittering )
- ( laughing )
- ( groaning )
( screaming )
- CONGRATULATIONS
ON YOUR BRAVERY.
HERE'S YOUR REWARD!
- ( gasping )
- OH!
- ( explosion )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, TENCHI?
- UM, NOTHING, I GUESS.
NOW YOU WERE TELLING ME
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOSHINAGA AND SUGANO.
- YEAH, WELL, THEY KEPT
ASKING IF I LIKE YOU, TENCHI.
I SAID, "HOW CAN YOU TELL?"
AND THEY'RE ALL,
"IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS."
KIND OF ANNOYING, ISN'T IT?
I GUESS I BETTER TRY
TO BE MORE SUBTLE ABOUT IT.
YOU PROBABLY DON'T LIKE IT.
I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
- NO, I DON'T MIND.  YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WORRY 'CAUSE OF THAT.
IT'S OKAY.
- OH!
- ( panting )
- ( groaning )
- ( whimpers )
- Yugi: HA!  PRETTY PATHETIC.
ONCE YOU LOSE UNITY,
YOU BECOME SO VULNERABLE.
IN FACT, YOU'RE HARDLY
EVEN WORTH THE EFFORT.
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
I CAN'T LOSE THIS EASILY,
NOT NOW TO THAT LITTLE RUNT!
- IT'S ALL OVER.
- OH, TENCHI.
- HUH?
- WHAT'S THAT, TENCHI?
- ( gasps )
- OH.
WOW.
- OH, TENCHI.
- ARE YOU THERE, LORD TENCHI?
- ( whimpering )
- WHAT IN THE WORLD?
- LORD TENCHI.
- TENCHI, PLEASE.
- NO, HE CAN'T HAVE THAT MUCH
POWER LEFT.
( gasps )
- NO, YUGI!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- ( whimpering )
- I'M HERE, YUGI.
WAKE UP, PLEASE.
- I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
THANKS, SASAMI.
- YUGI, WHAT'S HAPPENING
TO YOU?
- I STAYED ON THIS SIDE OF THE
WORLD JUST A LITTLE TOO LONG.
( groans )
- YOU LITTLE TWERP.
I AM RYOKO!
AND I AM NOT ONE
TO BE TRIFLED WITH.
- ( gasps )
DAMN.  NOT AGAIN.
- NICE TRY,
BUT NOW YOU'RE FINISHED, RYOKO.
- ( growls )
- ( gasps )
- IT'S YOU.
- YOU'RE VERY BRAVE, RYOKO,
AND DASHING.
- NOT DASHING.  NO, THAT'S
SOMETHING YOU SAY TO A MALE.
- YOUR REINFORCEMENTS
HAVE ARRIVED.
THAT'S A TWIST.
SO BE IT.
YOUR EXECUTION
IS TEMPORARILY POSTPONED.
( laughing )
- RYOKO.
- HUH?
- SEE YOU LATER.
- IT'S BEEN FUN.
- WHO ARE THEY?
AND WHAT IS ALL OF THIS ABOUT?
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I WANT TO KNOW.
- YEAH, SO DO WE ALL.
I CAN ONLY SAY
THERE IS A GIANT NET
OF CONSPIRACY
THAT IS CLOSING IN AROUND US.
- Ayeka: CONSPIRACY?
- YUGI.
WHERE ARE YOU?
- OH!  I GET IT.
RYO-OHKI, IT WAS JUST A DREAM.
RYO-OHKI.
- ( yawns )
- COME ON, RYO-OHKI.
LET'S GO HOME.
- ( meows )
- ( dialing telephone )
- ( ringing )
- EXCUSE ME,
BUT YOUR PHONE IS RINGING.
- ( groaning )
- MY BODY HURTS ALL OVER.
CHILL!
- UGH!
WHAT WAS THAT?
- ( panting )
- I MIGHT HAVE RETREATED
A BIT TOO SOON.
THEY'RE NOT QUITE AS EASY
AS I THOUGHT THEY WERE.
- THAT'S BECAUSE YOU TAKE RISKS.
I'M SURE YOU'D HAVE WON
IF YOU HADN'T
SPLIT YOURSELF
INTO TWO PARTS, YUGI.
- PERHAPS, BUT I DIDN'T WANT
HER TO SEE THE CARNAGE.
SASAMI'S MY FRIEND,
YOU SEE.
- WELL, AT LEAST HOTSUMA
AND TSUGARU WON THEIR TRUST.
SO IT'S NOT A COMPLETE LOSS.
- YES, WE'LL GO SLOW.
I HAD A GREAT TIME
WITH YOU, SASAMI.
REALLY.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meowing )
- I'M AYEKA.  SO THE DIMENSIONAL
TUNNEL IS BLOCKED,
AND THERE'S MONEY IN THE HOUSE
TO BUY THE TRAIN TICKETS.
BUT NOTHING CAN STOP ME
FROM TRYING TO SEE LORD TENCHI.
I'LL WALK ALL THE WAY
TO TOKYO IF I HAVE TO.
I KNOW ALL THE PURE-HEARTED
MAIDENS WHO LOOK FOR LOVE
AND BELIEVE IN LOVE
SHARE MY FEELINGS.
WHAT?  YOU'LL GIVE ME
A FREE RIDE TO TOKYO?
OH, THANK YOU, MISS MASAYO.
LET US GO HAND IN HAND
AFTER THE MEN WE LOVE.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF THE NEW
"TENCHI MUYO" SERIES--
"TOKYO OR BUST."