- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- ( gasps )
- A WHEEL OF LIGHT IS TURNING.
TURNING...
IT LOOKS SO WARM
AND SWEET.
FEELS JUST LIKE A DREAM.
LOOK, RYOKO'S DRIFTING AWAY
FROM THE OTHERS.
DREAM TIME WILL SOON BE OVER.
YES.
I WILL SOON END IT.
( chuckles )
- ( panting )
- ( exhales )
( grunts )
- HEY, BABY,
YOU LOOK LONELY.
BOYFRIEND STAND YOU UP?
- WE'LL HELP YOU
FORGET ABOUT HIM.
COME WITH US.
WE'LL HAVE SOME FUN TOGETHER.
- HEY, YOU WANT US TO BEG?
YOU'RE ALONE ANYWAY, RIGHT?
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
- YOUR BOYFRIEND
WON'T SHOW UP, SWEETIE.
SO COME ON WITH US.
- YEAH, HE STOOD YOU UP.
FACE IT.
- GET LOST.
- WHAT'S THAT?
I, UH, COULDN'T REALLY HEAR YOU.
- YEAH, WE DIDN'T MAKE YOU MAD
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT, DID WE?
- I SAID GET LOST!
- Both: UH...
HUH?
- ( breathes deeply, groans )
- RYOKO.
- ( gasps )
TENCHI, IT'S YOU.
- I'M WAITING.
JUST TAKE MY HAND.
- YOU WANT ME?
( groans softly )
HEY!  HMM?
( gasps slightly )
( grunts )
- ( both laughing )
( both scream )
- THAT IS RUDE.
- SHE WAS IN A HURRY.
- SOMEONE'S STALKING ME
VERY QUIETLY.
I CAN FEEL THEM THERE,
DEFINITELY.
WHERE ARE YOU?
WHERE ARE YOU HIDING?
WHERE WHERE WHERE?!
( gasps )
AAH!
( grunts )
OH, THIS ISN'T LIKE ME.
I'M GETTING CARELESS,
LOSING MY EDGE.
( gasps )
WHAT'S THIS?
AAH!
- ( gasps )
- WHAT IS IT, TENCHI?
- HUH?
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- UH, NO, NOTHING.
- WELL, AS I WAS SAYING,
WE DECIDED TO GO ON A TRIP
DURING SUMMER BREAK.
CLASSES WILL BE OVER, SO
THERE'S NO REASON TO STAY HERE.
IT COULD BE SO MUCH FUN.
DON'T YOU THINK, TENCHI?
- ( panting )
I KNOW THIS PLACE.
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
( gasps )
( grunts )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- THAT IS NO WAY TO GREET
AN OLD FRIEND,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU
ARE TRESPASSING.
- SO THIS WAS YOUR DOING,
EH, HOTSUMA?
- RYOKO, YOU LISTEN HERE.
- WHY SHOULD I?!
( grunts )
AAH!
- LOOK AT IT, RYOKO.
- ( gasps slightly )
LET ME GO.
- I SAID LOOK!
- ( groans )
WHAT?
WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS?
- THEY ARE BIO-ROID ENFORCERS
CREATED BY THE GALAXY PRINCE
TO HUNT DOWN
FIRST CLASS CRIMINALS.
THEY WORK IN SECRET,
AND THEY DESTROY THEIR PREY
WITHOUT LEAVING A TRACE.
- WOW!  YOU THINK
THERE ARE ENOUGH OF THEM?!
WHY WOULD THEY SEND THEM
DOWN HERE TO THIS PLANET?
- YOU SEEM TO HAVE
FORGOTTEN WHO YOU ARE.
- ( gasps )
- THEY'RE AFTER THE MOST
NOTORIOUS SPACE PIRATE
IN THE HISTORY OF THE GALAXY--
YOU.
- AND HOW WOULD YOU KNOW THAT?
- I HAVE MY SOURCES.
I LOST A BATTLE TO THEM
SIX MONTHS AGO,
AND I'VE BEEN HIDING HERE EVER
SINCE, WAITING FOR MY CHANCE.
- WHAT KIND OF CHANCE?
- THIS KIND.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR
SOMEONE LIKE YOU
TO TEAM UP WITH
AGAINST THE GALAXY POLICE
TO BLAZE INTO GLORIOUS BATTLE.
WE CAN SET THE WHOLE GALAXY
ON FIRE, RYOKO.
TAKE A LOOK AT MY TOWER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE GET OFF THIS PLANET?
YOU BELONG UP THERE
AMONG THE SHINING STARS.
- HMM...
- ( meows )
- WELL, SUMMER BREAK
IS JUST AROUND THE CORNER.
TIME JUST FLIES BY,
DOESN'T IT?
- UH-HUH. OH, AND MATSUNO SAID
SHE AND THE OTHERS
ARE GOING TO THE BEACH.
- THE BEACH, HUH?
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME SINCE I'VE
GONE DOWN TO THE OCEAN.
- DO YOU LIKE IT THERE?
- YEAH, I USED TO
GO THERE A LOT.
WHEN I WAS LITTLE,
I WENT WITH MY FAMILY.
I USED TO TAKE MY BIKE,
AND MY MOTHER WOULD WALK
WITH THIS BIG PARASOL.
THERE WAS A STEEP SLOPE,
AND AT THE BOTTOM,
THE OCEAN STRETCHED OUT AS FAR
AS YOU COULD SEE, SPARKLING.
JUST BEING THERE
WITH MY MOTHER...
THERE WAS SOMETHING
SPECIAL ABOUT IT.
IT'S THE KIND OF THING
YOU NEVER FORGET.
MY FATHER SAID I THREW A FIT
WHEN WE HAD TO LEAVE.
I COULD HAVE STAYED THERE
FOREVER.
- YOU'RE MAKING ME
WANNA GO THERE.
MM, JUST TO SEE THE WAVES
AND FEEL THE BREEZE.
- SAKUYA?
- HMM?
- MAYBE WE COULD GO THERE
TOGETHER SOMETIME.
- UH-HUH.
- IT'S KIND OF A LONG WAY,
YOU KNOW,
IF WE GO TO OKAYAMA.
BUT IT'D BE WORTH IT. I'M SURE
IT'S STILL JUST AS BEAUTIFUL.
- TENCHI...
MM.
CAN I RIDE YOUR BIKE
WHEN WE GET THERE?
- ( chuckles )
YOU BET!
- I CAN'T WAIT!
- LEAVE ME ALONE!
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT TROUBLE.
- ( gasps )
TENCHI...
YOU REALLY THINK YOU DON'T
NEED US ANYMORE?
YOU DON'T NEED ME ANYMORE?
NO NO.
IT CAN'T BE TRUE.
YOU DIDN'T MEAN IT THAT WAY.
I DON'T CARE WHAT ANYONE SAYS.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT...
BECAUSE IF I DID,
I'D BE LOST.
- RYOKO,
LET'S BLOW THIS PLANET.
- DON'T TELL ME WHAT TO DO. I
DON'T NEED A PARTNER OR A BOSS.
- THEY'LL HUNT YOU DOWN IF YOU
STAY HERE! YOU HAVE TO GO!
- I DON'T HAVE TO DO ANYTHING,
EXCEPT GET YOU OFF MY BACK!
AM I BEING CLEAR?!
( gasps )
- WATCH OUT!
IT'S A WEB MANEUVER!
- ( grunting )
I DON'T WANT YOUR HELP.
JUST GET OUT OF HERE!
- NOT WITHOUT YOU.
I NEED YOU AND YOU NEED ME.
- YEAH, RIGHT,
LIKE I NEED A DISEASE.
- THIS PLANET IS RUINING YOU.
PEOPLE USED TO FEAR YOU.
YOUR NAME SPREAD TERROR
THROUGHOUT THE ENTIRE GALAXY.
- JUST SHUT UP!
- YOU'RE A PIRATE, MY DEAR.
THAT'S YOUR DESTINY.
WHAT WE BOTH WANT CAN ONLY
BE GAINED THROUGH BLOOD,
FIRE AND DISASTER!
- YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ME!
- I KNOW YOU'RE WASTING YOURSELF
ON THIS PITIFUL LITTLE PLANET,
WHILE POWER AND GLORY
AWAIT YOU OUT IN SPACE.
- I'VE BEEN THERE!
SPACE IS BIG AND EMPTY.
I BELONG RIGHT HERE,
RIGHT ON THIS PLANET...
BECAUSE THERE'S SOMETHING--
SOMETHING I LOST.
( groans )
- ( chuckles softly )
- THAT GIRL AND TENCHI...
I JUST CAN'T TAKE IT.
( screams )
( panting )
- ( chuckles softly )
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU JUST PROVED MY POINT.
YOU DON'T BELONG HERE.
COME WITH ME, RYOKO.
- ( chuckles )
PRINCESS AYEKA,
HAVING A HARD TIME
FALLING ASLEEP, ARE YOU?
- YES. HOW DO YOU KNOW
MY NAME, PRAY TELL?
WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU?
- A SORCERER.
- HUH?
- AHEM...
PRINCESS, I'VE COME HERE
TO HELP YOU UNTANGLE
THE RIDDLES THAT HAVE
BEEN TROUBLING YOU.
- WHAT RIDDLES?
- A MAN CAPTURED YOUR HEART,
AND HE KEEPS IT LIKE
A BIRD IN A CAGE.
- ( gasps )
- TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
LOOK DEEPLY
AND SEE THE TRUTH.
NO MATTER HOW MUCH YOU
MAY LOVE HIM,
HE WILL NEVER
COME BACK TO YOU.
AND YOU KNOW THE REASON.
- ( water trickling )
- HE'S FOUND A NEW WORLD
AND A NEW LOVE
IN A LAND FAR AWAY FROM HERE.
PEOPLE CHANGE, PRINCESS.
- IT'S NOT TRUE.
- BUT YOU KNOW IT IS.
- LIAR LIAR LIAR!
TENCHI ISN'T LIKE THAT.
HE'S NOT, HE'S NOT!
HE'LL COME BACK TO ME,
I KNOW IT.
- OH...
DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE THAT,
OR ARE YOU JUST TRYING
TO CONVINCE YOURSELF
BECAUSE YOU HAVE SO MANY DOUBTS?
- I BELIEVE IN HIM.
- WELL, THEN ALL YOU
HAVE TO DO IS ASK HIM.
THEN YOU'LL KNOW
FOR CERTAIN, PRINCESS.
I'LL BE HERE TO HELP YOU,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
CALL HIM, AYEKA.
- ( gasps )
WAIT!  DON'T GO!
- (Sorcerer's voice) WELL, THEN
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS ASK HIM.
THEN YOU'LL KNOW
FOR CERTAIN, PRINCESS.
- TENCHI...
- AWW...
I NEED THE PHONE.
- OH.
- ( laughs )
- ( keys beeping )
- ( line ringing )
- Tenchi:
Yes, this is Tenchi.
- HI, TENCHI!
IT'S SASAMI.
RISE AND SHINE!
IT'S TIME FOR BREAKFAST.
AND NONE OF THOSE
FROZEN WAFFLES.
EAT SOMETHING FRESH
THAT'S GOOD FOR YOU.
WHAT?  UH-HUH.
WELL, YEAH,
WE'RE DOING GREAT.
UH-HUH.
OH, AYEKA'S HERE TOO.
I'LL GIVE HER THE PHONE,
SO YOU CAN SAY HELLO.
HOLD ON.
HERE SHE IS.
TAKE IT.
- ( shakily )
SASAMI, I--
- GO ON,
IT'S LONG-DISTANCE.
- HELLO, TENCHI.
IT SEEMS LIKE A LONG TIME
SINCE WE'VE TALKED.
- Long time? What do you mean?
We saw each other yesterday.
- I KNOW, BUT IT FEELS
LIKE AGES SOMEHOW.
- Ayeka, I'd like to and all,
but I gotta get to school.
- WAIT, I WANTED
TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
- SURE.  FIRE AWAY.
- Well, I know you have
new friends at school.
How are you getting along
with them?
- JUST FINE.  WHY?
- THAT GIRL--
IS IT FINE WITH HER TOO?
- Uh, what?
- YOU KNOW WHO I MEAN.
SAKUYA.
- ( doorbell rings )
- HUH?
EXCUSE ME.
I HAVE TO GET THE DOOR.
- Uh, wait!  Tenchi!
- SORRY!
I'LL BE JUST A MINUTE.
- Sakuya: YOU'RE LATE.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO RUN TO SCHOOL AGAIN.
- ( whimpers )
- Tenchi:
What's our first class today?
- Well, you remember.
Our Middle Old Japanese.
- I think we'll make it.
- AH, YOUR TIE IS CROOKED AGAIN.
- AYEKA, I'LL CALL YOU
BACK LATER, OKAY?
OKAY, LET'S GO.
YOU READY?
- MM-HMM.
- OH.  I'M SORRY, AYEKA.
- FAREWELL.
- ( chuckles )
- GO.
YOU'VE SERVED YOUR PURPOSE.
( chuckles )
GOOD-BYE, DEAR RYOKO.
- ( upbeat music playing )
- ( people singing in Japanese )
- YEAH!
( growls )
MEOW.
- HELLO, I'M AYEKA.
CONGRATULATIONS, MIHOSHI AND
KIYONE, FOR YOUR PROMOTION.
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
BUT I'LL MISS YOU VERY MUCH
WHILE YOU'RE ON
YOUR ASSIGNMENT ON PLUTO.
MISS WASHU HAS LOCKED HERSELF
IN HER LAB, AND RYOKO IS GONE.
SO OUR DINING TABLE-- WHICH
HAS ALWAYS BEEN SO CROWDED,
IS NOW DESERTED AND LONELY.
OH, LORD TENCHI,
WHAT HAS BECOME OF US?
THE NEXT EPISODE OF
THE NEW TENCHI MUYO SERIES...