- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( horn blows )
- ( laughing )
- Woman: I'M GETTING OFF HERE
AND THAT'LL BE THE LAST TIME
I SEE YOU.
- ( P.A. announcer
speaks in Japanese )
- IT'S GOODBYE.
- WAIT.  TAKE THIS.
- OH!
- I WANT YOU TO MARRY ME.
- ( gasps )
- ( sobs )
- Man on TV: That concludes
the "Juyo Line of Love."
- THAT PROGRAM IS SO SAPPY
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
- THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT
SO WONDERFUL. ( sniffles )
IT'S SO HEART-WRENCHING.
- I'M GLAD IT HAD
A HAPPY ENDING.  AREN'T YOU?
- YES, IT'S BEAUTIFUL
TO BE CLOSE TO THE ONE YOU LOVE.
- Sasami: OKAY, THAT'S ABOUT
ENOUGH TELEVISION.
LET'S TURN IT OFF.
- NO WAY, SASAMI.  "THE WHITE
SNOWFALL" IS STARTING NOW.
IT'S MY FAVORITE SOAP.
ALL THE CHARACTERS HAVE AMNESIA.
- GREAT.  ARE THEY ALL
OBSESSED LIKE YOU?
AYEKA, YOU'VE GOTTA TURN THAT
OFF.  IT'S A TOTAL YAWN
AND MIHOSHI ASKED ME
TO TAPE A RERUN
OF "SPACE POLICE POLICEMAN"
FOR HER.
- "SPACE POLICE POLICEMAN,"
YOU'RE JOKING.
- UNH-UNH.  IN TOKYO,
SHE TOOK A PART-TIME JOB
PLAYING A SPACE VILLAIN
IN THIS WEIRD "POLICEMAN" SHOW.
- THAT'S HER PROBLEM.  I'M NOT
GOING TO MISS "WHITE SNOWFALL."
- Ryoko: OH, NO.
I ALMOST FORGOT.
IT'S TIME FOR "WILD SAMURAI'S
LONE JOURNEY 5."
- ( gasps ) HEY, WHAT DO
YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- IS THERE A PROBLEM?
- YES, YOU.
I'M NOT GOING TO WATCH
SOME DERANGED SAMURAI SHOW.
IT IS TIME FOR MY SOAP.
NOW DON'T GRAB MY REMOTE.
IT'S BAD MANNERS.
- ( both grunting )
- DON'T YOU EVER GET ENOUGH
OF THOSE WHINY SOAPS, HUH?
THEY'RE NAUSEATING.
- YOU AND YOUR SAMURAI SHOWS
ARE GREAT DRAMA, RIGHT?
PERFECT FOR A TOTAL PSYCHO.
- ( meows )
- WHAT?  YOU WANNA PLAY
A VIDEO GAME?
- DON'T INTERRUPT OUR FIGHT.
- HERE WE GO.
- SO GINGERBREAD'S MADE
FROM GINGER?
- THAT'S RIGHT, AND GINGER'S
IN ONE OF THE FIVE FOOD GROUPS.
- WASHU, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
PUT IT BACK
ON "WILD SAMURAI
LONE JOURNEY 5."
- AND MISS THIS?  NO WAY.
"SCIENCE FOR EGGHEADS" IS
MY FAVORITE SHOW.  IT ROCKS.
- IF IT WERE UP TO ME,
I'D WATCH "MR. HOME EC'S
THREE-MINUTE COOKING CORNER."
HOW ABOUT YOU, AZAKA?
- SAMURAIS DON'T WATCH
TELEVISION.
- HEY, I'M GOING TO MISS
MY FAVORITE SHOW.
- WASHU, PUT ON THE "SAMURAI."
- CALM DOWN, EVERYONE.
I HAVE A NEW INVENTION
THAT WILL SOLVE THE SITUATION.
IT'S PURE GENIUS, OF COURSE.
MULTIPLE TELEVISION.
- GET OUT.  THAT THING
IS SO PUNY,
YOU'D NEED TO BE AN ANT
TO WATCH IT.
- THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.
TAKE A LOOK.
- ( gasping )
- YOU SEE?
NEVER DOUBT MY BRAINPOWER.
AND THERE'S MORE.
I PLANTED DNA FROM
SOME MULTIPLYING MITOCHONDRIA
IN THE TV'S HARD DRIVE.
NOW YOU CAN ALL WATCH WHATEVER
PROGRAM YOU LIKE AND QUIT
BUGGING ME ALL THE TIME.
- YOU INVENTED SOMETHING USEFUL.
WHAT A CONCEPT.
- YOU REALLY ARE A GENIUS,
WASHU.
- THAT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN
TELLING YOU.
ONLY YOU CAN MAKE THAT
SUPER GENIUS.  ( laughing )
- UH, EXCUSE ME.
DON'T YOU THINK THERE'S
A LITTLE TOO MANY OF THEM?
- ( gasping )
- WHOOPS!
- ( explosion )
- UGH.  HUH?
- THANK YOU, AZAKA AND KAMIDAKE.
- OUR PLEASURE.
IT'S OUR DUTY AS GUARDIANS
TO PROTECT YOU
FROM ALL HARM, PRINCESS.
- WE WILL GO ANYWHERE ANYTIME
TO PROTECT YOU FROM DANGER.
- THAT'S HEARTWARMING.
MEANWHILE, I'M MISSING
"WILD SAMURAI LONE JOURNEY 5."
- HUH?
- LOOK THERE ON TV.
- ( fanfare plays )
- LORD TENCHI!
- TENCHI!
- Good afternoon, everyone.
I'm bringing you
this action news report live
from a suburb of Tokyo.
- DUMB REPORTER.
MOVE SO I CAN SEE TENCHI.
- This North Okutama ruin
was discovered near the fissure
created by an earthquake
three months ago.
According to researchers here,
this ruin is believed
to be 3,500 years old.
The primary excavation
was just completed yesterday.
- AHA!  SO TENCHI'S
IN NORTH OKUTAMA NOW.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO
GO VISIT HIM ALONE.
- AZAKA!
- ON MY WAY.
- ( Ryoko screams )
- ( Azaka grunts )
- ( laughing )
- ( gasps )
YOU SNEAKY WITCH!
- HOORAY!  I GOT RYOKO STUCK
ON HER SIDE OF THE TUNNEL.
THAT MEANS I CAN HAVE A PRIVATE
RENDEZVOUS WITH LORD TENCHI.
- ( laughs )
- HEY, COME BACK HERE, AYEKA!
- STUDENTS, BEHAVE YOURSELVES
AND STAY TOGETHER...
- HE TREATS US ALL LIKE
WE'RE STILL IN GRADE SCHOOL
OR DIDN'T YOU NOTICE?
- YEAH.
- Girl: WHAT'S WRONG, SAKUYA?
YOU SEEM SO QUIET LATELY.
EVER SINCE YOU TOOK THAT DAY
OFF, YOU'VE BEEN ACTING STRANGE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
- BET I KNOW.
YOU ATE TOO MUCH AND YOU
PUT ON SOME WEIGHT, RIGHT?
- THAT'S YOUR PROBLEM, NOT HERS.
- HOW'D YOU KNOW THAT?
- LISTEN, SAKUYA.
MAYBE WE CAN HELP.
IF SOMETHING HAPPENED,
TELL US WHAT IT IS.
- WELL...
IT'S NOTHING REALLY.
NOTHING I WANT TO TALK ABOUT.
SO LET'S GO.
- HEY, TENCHI, TENCHI.
- HUH?
- COME ON, BUDDY,
WE GOTTA HURRY.
THE REST OF THE CLASS
HAS GONE AHEAD OF US.
- BUT MAYBE WE CAN FIND
A TREASURE HERE,
LIKE SOME OLD KING'S SCEPTER
COVERED IN JEWELS.
OR MAYBE WE COULD DIG UP
SOME GOLDEN POTTERY.
- IF SOMETHING'S MADE OUT OF
GOLD, THEN IT'S NOT POTTERY.
ANYWAY, THERE'S NO TREASURES
AROUND HERE.
JUST A BUNCH OF OLD JUNK.
HUH?
OF COURSE, IT'S STILL
INTERESTING, EH, TENCHI?
- HUH?  WELL, IT DOES MAKE YOU
WONDER, DOESN'T IT?
WHAT KIND OF PEOPLE COULD HAVE
LIVED HERE 3,500 YEARS AGO?
- ACTUALLY, I KNOW A LOT
ABOUT THAT.
3,500 WOULD BE
THE AZUCHI-MOMOYAMA PERIOD.
- IT'S IN THE JOMON ERA.
FOR SURE.
- HA!
THOUGHT YOU WERE SO SMART!
WHO'S THE CLOWN NOW?
- CAN'T YOU SEE I SAID THAT
ON PURPOSE JUST
TO MAKE YOU LAUGH?
- YOU'RE GONNA BREAK THIS THING!
- ( screaming )
- UGH!  BETTER WATCH OUT
FOR THAT LAST STEP.
- WOW.  WHERE ARE WE?
AM I STILL UMANOSUKE?
UH-HUH.
- HUH?  THAT PLACE.
WHAT IS IT?
- ( laughing )
IT LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE JUST
INVADED YOUR BEDROOM.
DID YOU KNOW THAT, YUKI?
- THIS IS NOT MY BEDROOM
AT ALL.
IN FACT, IT'S MY GRAVE
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW.
- Tenchi: COULD THIS REALLY BE
FROM THE JOMON ERA?
- YEAH, WE JUST MADE
A HISTORIC DISCOVERY.
I HEREBY DECLARE THIS
THE AMAGASAKI SHRINE,
AFTER MYSELF OF COURSE,
WHICH MEANS THAT NOW I'M FAMOUS.
- HOW ARE YOU GONNA GET FAMOUS
IF YOU CAN'T GET OUT OF HERE?
WE ARE UNDER THE GROUND.
WHAT IF WE'RE ALL
STUCK HERE FOREVER?
WHAT IF WE HAVE TO LIVE HERE
TILL WE'RE OLD WITH BEARDS
AND EVERYTHING?
- WELL, THERE YOU GO.  ANOTHER
DAY JUST LIKE ALL THE OTHERS.
EH, TENCHI?
- WHAT'S THAT, UMANOSUKE?
DID YOU SAY SOMETHING THERE?
- UMANOSUKE SAID TODAY'S
ANOTHER DAY JUST LIKE
ALL THE OTHER DAYS.
HE SAYS THAT EVERY DAY.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR HIM?
- NO, I THOUGHT HE SAID
TODAY'S LIKE ALL OTHER DAYS.
OF COURSE TODAY IS LIKE
ALL THE OTHER DAYS,
JUST AS BORING
AS THE REST OF 'EM.
- ( laughing )
- ( screams )
I CAN'T TAKE IT.
WE'VE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE!
- LORD TENCHI, I'M COMING TO YOU
ON "THE JUYO LINE OF LOVE"
JUST LIKE ON TV.
- ( loud rumbling )
- OOH!
OH!
I'M NOT GETTING OFF HERE!
STOP PUSHING ME!
TENCHI!
- ( meows )
- I THINK THIS IS THE BEGINNING
OF THE AMAGASAKI EMPIRE.
- WITH YOU AS EMPEROR,
I DON'T THINK SO.
- ( gasps )
WHAT IS THIS?
OH!
- WE HAVE SEALED THE EVIL ONE
IN THIS STYGIAN VAULT
FOR ALL ETERNITY.
HENCEFORTH, NONE SHALL APPROACH
THIS MYSTIC CHAMBER.
HE WHO ATTEMPTS
TO BREAK THE SEAL
SHALL BE STRICKEN
WITH DISASTER.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- HEY, ARE YOU OKAY, TENCHI?
- YOU GOT A HEADACHE?
- IT'S NOTHING.
I'M JUST A LITTLE DIZZY.
I SAW SOMETHING, A VISION.
BUT WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
- WHERE IS HE?
TENCHI CAN'T JUST BE MISSING.
- HE IS.
SO ARE UMANOSUKE AND KAZUHIKO.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- DID YOU HEAR THE NEWS?
TENCHI'S GROUP HAS DISAPPEARED.
- THEY PROBABLY WENT
TO GET A PIZZA.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
- ALL YOU EVER THINK OF IS FOOD.
- TENCHI.
- IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT MAYBE TENCHI'S FALLEN
INTO THE MAGNIFICENT WORLD.
- EXCUSE ME.
PARDON ME, MA'AM,
BUT I'M LOOKING
FOR MY LORD TENCHI.
I MEAN, A STUDENT NAMED TENCHI.
- HUH?
TENCHI?
- IT'S YOU, MIHOSHI.
- WOW, PRINCESS AYEKA.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
( screams )
- THEY'RE ANCIENT RELICS,
MIHOSHI!
- I KNOW IT'S A STONE CRYPT,
AND AN EVIL ONE IS IN IT.
( grunts )
IT'S BROKEN!
- ( laughs )
I'D STILL BE SLEEPING DEEPLY
IF THAT EARTHQUAKE
THREE MONTHS AGO HADN'T DROPPED
A HUGE ROCK ON MY SARCOPHAGUS.
- AND WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING?
- I'M NOT PLANNING ANYTHING,
BUT THERE IS AN INTERESTING BOY
I'VE SET MY SIGHTS UPON.
- TENCHI, ISN'T IT DANGEROUS
IF YOU GET TOO CLOSE TO IT?
- I THINK IT'S OKAY.
- ( laughs )
WELL, I FOUND A GOOD SEAT.
THIS WILL BE THE THRONE OF THE
KING OF THE AMAGASAKI DYNASTY.
YOU WILL BE THE MINISTERS
OF MY IMPERIAL EMPIRE.
- ( sighs )
- ALL RIGHT, YOU CAN APPROACH
THE ROYAL THRONE.
- HEY, AMAGASAKI!
- OH!
- ( gasps ) AZAKA, KAMIDAKE.
WHY ARE THEY HERE?
- Amagasaki: YOU TWO LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE GETTING SMALLER,
LIKE LITTLE INSECTS.
GUESS THIS IS THE WAY
THE WORLD LOOKS
WHEN YOU BECOME
A GREAT ROYAL MONARCH.
DON'T WORRY.
YOU'RE STILL MY FRIENDS.
JUST CALL ME
YOUR ROYAL HIGHNESS.
- STOP BABBLING FOR A MINUTE
AND LOOK UNDERNEATH YOUR BUTT.
- WHAT?  UNDER MY BUTT?
HMM...
HUH?  HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
( screams )
- THE ANCIENT CRYPT
IS NO LONGER SEALED.
THE EVIL ONE HAS ESCAPED
THE SEAL OF JURAI.
- JURAI?  SO THAT THING
CAME FROM PLANET JURAI.
I WARN YOU.  RETURN TO
THE STONE CRYPT VOLUNTARILY
OR YOU WILL BE FORCED
TO DO SO.
- STONE CRYPT.  WHAT THE HECK
ARE THEY TALKING ABOUT?
- FEAR NOT.
I'LL HANDLE THEM.
- WAIT, AMAGASAKI.  YOU DON'T
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DEALING WITH.
- HEY, HAVE A LITTLE LAUGH.
HERE'S A TIP.
DANCE AROUND AND FORGET
ABOUT THAT CREEPY CRYPT.
- UNACCEPTABLE RESPONSE.
- DANGEROUS ACTION.
SHIFT TO ATTACK MODE.
- ( screaming )
- LORD TENCHI, WHERE ARE YOU?
- TENCHI!
- HOW COULD TENCHI DISAPPEAR
WITHOUT A WORD?
HE WOULDN'T DO THAT,
WOULD HE, KIYONE?
UNLESS HE TRIPPED AND FELL
INTO A HOLE OR SOMETHING.
- SOUNDS LIKE SOMETHING
YOU'D DO.
- THAT'S NOT FAIR AT ALL.
I MAY BE A LITTLE CLUMSY,
BUT I DON'T GO AROUND
FALLING IN HOLES.
( screaming )
- I'M TOO YOUNG TO DIE.  I DON'T
WANNA GO IN SOME CREEPY CRYPT.
- ( panting )
- HUH?
- IT'S A DEAD END.
- THIS IS YOUR FINAL WARNING.
RETURN TO YOUR CRYPTS.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT US TO GO
INSIDE OF SOME OLD COFFIN FOR?
THAT'S TOTALLY SICK.
- THEY'VE GOT US MIXED UP
WITH AN EVIL DEMON
WHO'S SUPPOSED TO BE
IN THAT CRYPT.
- OH, THIS IS A DRAG!
- WARNING TIME OVER.
TERMINATE THEM.
- ( screaming )
- AYEKA!
- WHY, LORD TENCHI,
I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
- AND IT'S BECAUSE OF ME
THAT WE GOT HERE.
- YOU MEAN BECAUSE
OF YOUR CLUMSINESS?
- YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO POINT
THAT OUT, YOU KNOW?
OH, IT LOOKS JUST LIKE
THE SECRET FACE OF ORGON.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD'S THAT?
- YOU KNOW, THE VILLAINS
ON "SPACE POLICE POLICEMAN,"
THE TV SHOW.
THIS LOOKS JUST LIKE
THEIR UNDERGROUND HIDEOUT.
- THIS IS NOT TV,
SO CAN IT.
- THESE INTRUDERS ARE AGENTS
OF THE EVIL ONE.
- THEY MUST BE EXPUNGED AT ONCE.
COMMENCE TERMINATION PROTOCOL.
- TENCHI, THOSE ARE
JURAI GUARDIANS.
- OH!
- UGH!
- I AM AYEKA, THE FIRST PRINCESS
OF THE JURAI ROYAL FAMILY.
HOW DARE YOU ATTACK
A TRUE JURAI PRINCESS.
I ORDER YOU TO STOP THIS
AT ONCE.
- BIO VERIFICATION COMPLETE.
SHE IS THE FIRST PRINCESS
OF THE JURAI ROYAL FAMILY.
- OF COURSE I AM.
NOW GO AWAY.
- YES, MA'AM.
- AS YOU COMMAND.
- YOU REALLY SAVED ME, AYEKA.
- WHY, IT'S MY PLEASURE, TENCHI.
I'D DO ANYTHING FOR YOU.
NOW WHAT I WANT TO KNOW
IS WHY ARE THERE GUARDIANS
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS,
AND THEY'RE SUCH OLD MODELS.
- THAT'S NOT ALL, AYEKA.
LOOK OVER THERE.
- THAT'S JURAIEAN.
IT'S A SEALED SHRINE.
- SO ARE YOU GONNA END IT NOW?
- THAT WOULD SPOIL THE FUN,
WOULDN'T IT?
BUT WHAT ELSE
CAN YOU EXPECT
WHEN THE JURAI ROYAL FAMILY
GETS INVOLVED?
- GUARDIANS.
- HMM.
YOU LOOK LIKE
AZAKA AND KAMIDAKE.
- Both: TERMINATE!  TERMINATE!
TERMINATE!  TERMINATE!
- HUH?
- WHAT ARE THEY SAYING?
- TERMINATE!  TERMINATE!
TERMINATE!  TERMINATE!
- WHY ARE THEY SHOOTING AT US?
- YOU WERE POKING AT THEM,
MIHOSHI.
YOU MUST HAVE MADE THEM MAD.
- BUT I DIDN'T POKE THEM HARD.
- TERMINATE!  TERMINATE!
TERMINATE!  TERMINATE!
- STOP NOW.
I AM THE FIRST PRINCESS
OF THE JURAI ROYAL FAMILY.
- TERMINATE! TERMINATE!
- IMPOSSIBLE!  HOW CAN
GUARDIANS REFUSE MY ORDERS?
IT'S HERESY.
- BACK ME UP, MIHOSHI.
- TERMINATE!  TERMINATE!
- I WOULD BACK YOU UP,
BUT I LOST MY GUN.
WHERE DID I PUT THAT THING?
- MIHOSHI.
- OH!
- TERMINATE! TERMINATE!
- ( screaming )
- YOU DARE ATTACK LORD TENCHI.
YOU'RE HISTORY!
- ALL RIGHT!
- YOU'RE HOT, PRINCESS.
- TERMINATE!  TERMINATE!
- TERMINATE!
- HUH?!
- ( all scream )
- WATCH OUT, AYEKA.
- ( screams )
- KAMIDAKE.
- AZAKA, SIR.
- BLAST OFF!
WE'RE ON OUR WAY.
- WOW!
- ( meows )
- ( screaming )
- HANG ON, AYEKA.
- TERMINATE!  TERMINATE!
- ( groans )
I CAN'T HOLD OUT ANY LONGER.
- WE'RE GOING IN.
- TEENAGERS.
- LORD TENCHI, I'M SORRY.
- AYEKA, NO!
- WHOA!
- HUH?
- Azaka:
WE HAVE ARRIVED!
- AZAKA, KAMIDAKE,
AM I GLAD TO SEE YOU.
IT IS OUR DUTY AS GUARDIANS
TO PROTECT YOU
FROM ALL HARM,
PRINCESS.
- WE WILL GO ANYWHERE, ANYTIME
TO PROTECT YOU FROM DANGER.
- HMM.
- TERMINATE!  TERMINATE!
- TIME FOR ACTION, KAMIDAKE.
- YES, SIR.
- TERMINATE!
- ELIMINATE!
- ( grunting )
- IT'S SO WEIRD.  THEY LOOK
LIKE A BUNCH OF BIG LOGS
BUMPING INTO EACH OTHER.
- THEY CHARGE WITH A LOT
OF OOMPH,
BUT IT IS A WEIRD BATTLE.
- FINISH THEM,
AZAKA, KAMIDAKE.
- Both: YES, MA'AM.
- OPEN FIRE.
- RIGHT.
- ( screaming )
- WOW!  IT'S JUST LIKE
"SPACE POLICE POLICEMAN."
- WOULD YOU FORGET
ABOUT THAT TV SHOW ALREADY?
- THIS TOMB DEFINITELY BELONGS
TO OUR PLANET JURAI.
- INDEED.
- WHAT'S IT DOING HERE ON EARTH?
- I DON'T KNOW.  HOWEVER,
THERE WAS SOMEONE SEALED INSIDE.
SEALED BY A JURAIEAN
LORD OR PRIEST,
BUT WAS IT FOR GOOD OR EVIL?
THAT'S THE MYSTERY.
- Tenchi:
SOMETHING CAME FROM PLANET JURAI
TO EARTH 3,500 YEARS AGO.
WHAT WAS IT?
- WHERE WERE YOU AND WHAT HAVE
YOU BEEN DOING ALL THIS TIME?
I ALREADY TOLD YOU.
THERE'S A ROYAL TOMB
OF THE AMAGASAKI EMPIRE,
AND WE WERE THERE INSIDE--
- COME ON!  IF YOU'RE GONNA LIE,
AT LEAST COME UP
WITH A BETTER STORY THAN THAT.
- WELL, THAT WAS ENTERTAINING.
- HOPE IT DIDN'T STIR UP
UNPLEASANT MEMORIES.
- NOT REALLY. ( laughs )
I CAN'T WAIT
TO RAISE MY CASTLE
TO THE SURFACE
OF THIS PLANET.
OF COURSE, THERE ARE MANY
DELICIOUS PREPARATIONS
WE HAVE TO MAKE FIRST.
( laughing )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meowing )
- HOWDY.  I'M RYOKO.
YOU KNOW WHAT, TENCHI?
I CAN BE REAL FEMININE
IF I PUT SOME MAKEUP ON.
I KNOW I CAN LOOK STUNNING
IF I TRY.
LOOK AT ME.
AREN'T I GORGEOUS?
YOU WANNA SEE?
YOU DO WANNA SEE, DON'T YOU?
I KNOW YOU DO.  ALL RIGHT,
YOU CAN SEE ME TOMORROW
WHEN WE HAVE A DATE.
YOU AND ME.
I'M WARNING YOU THOUGH.
I'LL BE SO STUNNING,
THAT YOU MAY BE
KNOCKED OUT COLD.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF
NEW "TENCHI MUYO" SERIES
"RYOKO'S BIG DATE."