- ( theme song playing )
- ( sighs )
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S NO BETTER REWARD
THAN A CUP OF STEAMING TEA.
- ( phone rings )
- HELLO.
TENCHI MASAKI.
- Sasami: TENCHI,
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME.
- IS THIS SASAMI?
- EVERYBODY'S AFTER ME.
- MEOW.
- SASAMI, WHAT'S UP?
SO WHAT'S HAPPENED?
HOW COME YOU'RE SO UPSET?
- ( sighs ) ALL RIGHT.
IT ALL BEGAN
WHEN RYO-OHKI AND I
WERE PERFORMING SOME TRICKS
FOR PEOPLE ON THE STREET
AND MADE
QUITE A BIT OF MONEY.
- ( applause )
- ( coins dinging )
- THE NEXT THING
I KNEW,
EVERYONE AT HOME
WAS TRYING TO STEAL IT.
- REALLY?
- MM-HMM.
- ( insects chirping )
- ( bird hooting )
- ( Sasami breathing deeply )
- MEOW.
MEOW.
- ( girls gasp )
- WAIT A MINUTE.
THERE ARE TOO MANY HANDS HERE.
HA!
- ( all shouting )
- Ryoko: STOP IT.
- ( sighs )
- MEOW?
- ( girls moaning )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
CRAWLING AROUND HERE
AT THIS TIME OF NIGHT?
- ME?  WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- HEY, WHY ARE ANY OF YOU HERE?
IT'S LATE.
- MEOW, MEOW, MEOW.
- WHEN I WOKE UP, I REALIZED
I NEEDED SOME CHANGE.
I KNEW
YOU HAD MONEY.
I FIGURED YOU WOULDN'T MIND
IF I BORROWED IT.
- ( giggles )
SASAMI, I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND.
I NEEDED THE MONEY TO RETRIEVE
THE GALAXY POLICE IDENTIFICATION
AND HANDCUFFS
THAT I PAWNED LAST WEEK.
- IF WE DON'T RETRIEVE
THEM VERY SOON,
THEY'RE GONNA SELL THEM.
THAT WOULD BE
PRETTY EMBARRASSING WHEN WE
GO BACK TO HEADQUARTERS.
I DON'T KNOW IF WE COULD
EVER EXPLAIN IT.
- I NEEDED THE MONEY
FOR MY LATEST EXPERIMENT.
I'M A FEW BYTES SHY
OF A MOTHERBOARD,
IF YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN.
- IT IS MY DUTY AS A WOMAN
TO MAINTAIN MY APPEARANCE
AND STAY BEAUTIFUL
FOR THE MAN I LOVE,
AND THEREFORE
I'M DUTY-BOUND
TO BUY THIS SEVEN-ITEM
BEAUTY CARE SET.
- HUH?
- SASAMI, THE FACT
OF THE MATTER IS,
YOU DON'T PLAN
TO SPEND THAT MONEY.
LET ME HAVE IT.
- WE'RE DESPERATE.
WE'RE COMPLETELY
BROKE, SASAMI.
- WE'LL PAY EVERY YEN BACK,
REALLY.
- I'LL BE SO GRATEFUL.
- IT WOULD JUST BE
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
- ( whimpering )
- PLEASE.
- PLEASE, SASAMI..
- ( Sasami screams )
ANYWAY, THAT'S WHY
I CAME TO SEE YOU.
- MEOW, MEOW.
- THAT'S AWFUL.
THEY'RE ALL BEING
SO GREEDY AND SELFISH.
BUT WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
ABOUT IT, SASAMI?
YOU HAVE TO GO BACK SOMETIME.
YOU CAN'T STAY HERE FOREVER.
I'M GOING TO BE LEAVING
IN THE MORNING TO GO TO SCHOOL.
- I KNOW.
OH.
- ( distant horns honking )
- ( gasps )
I COULD SPEND IT ALL.
- HUH?
- ( Yugi laughing )
I HAVE A SOLUTION
TO YOUR PROBLEM, SASAMI.
OH, YES.
WHY DON'T YOU COME
AND PLAY WITH ME?
IT'LL GIVE YOU A CHANCE
TO SEE MY WORLD.
TSUGARU.
- ( laughs )
COME HERE, TENCHI.
YOU'VE GOT TO SEE THIS.
- HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
- LOOK.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
- IT'S ALL MADE OF CHOCOLATE.
WOW.
- MEOW.
MEOW!
MEOW.
- COME BACK, RYO-OHKI.
- MEOW!
( screaming )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
( giggles )
( laughs )
THAT'S A BUNCH OF CARROTS
YOU HARVESTED.
- ( both laughing )
- HUH?  WHAT IS IT?
- OH, NOTHING MUCH.
I WAS JUST THINKING,
IT'S ALMOST LIKE
WE'RE HAVING A DATE.
- OH?
MM.
- ( chuckles )
- MEOW?
- SO WHY DON'T WE CHECK OUT
THE STORES ACROSS THE STREET?
- Tenchi: GOOD IDEA.
- MM?
MEOW.
MEOW, MEOW.
- ( chuckles )
- HUH?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER,
SASAMI?
- OH, NOTHING.
I'M JUST JUMPY.
OH, MY,
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW MANY PRETTY THINGS
THESE STORES HAVE.
- SASAMI, SLOW DOWN,
WILL YOU?
- YO!  COME ON, TENCHI.
YOU'RE REALLY OUT OF SHAPE.
YOU NEED MORE EXERCISE.
- MEOW, MEOW.
- ( Sasami sighs )
OH.
( giggles )
HMM.
- ( panting )
SASAMI?
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
SASAMI!
- HEY, LOOK.
SO PRETTY.
MM.
- HELLO.  DID YOU FIND
SOMETHING YOU LIKE?
- UH...
- YOU SHOULD TRY IT ON.
EVERYTHING'S ON SALE,
HALF OFF.
- MEOW!
- WHAT IN THE WORLD?
- THAT'S QUITE A TEMPER.
HAVE I DONE
SOMETHING WRONG?
- THIS IS WEIRD.
- MEOW!
- I DON'T KNOW.
THIS DOESN'T USUALLY HAPPEN.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL KEEP MY DISTANCE.
IF YOU FIND SOMETHING
YOU LIKE, JUST LET ME KNOW.
- HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU TODAY?
- MEOW.
- AH, I TURN MY BACK
FOR A MINUTE,
AND SHE DISAPPEARS.
HUH?  WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I WAS WORRIED.
- HOW POLITE.
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
- SAKUYA, I'M SURPRISED.
- I WAS HOPING
WE MIGHT HAVE A TALK.
- OH, YEAH?
I'M KIND OF BUSY, SAKUYA.
- I JUST WANT YOU
TO WALK WITH ME A LITTLE BIT.
- UH, OKAY.
- ( quiet tune playing )
- HUH?
- MEOW?
- OH, WOW.
FABULOUS.
HUH?
( gasps )
- MEOW.
MEOW.
- MEOW, MEOW.
- ( birds chirping )
- Ryoko: MY STOMACH CAN'T TAKE
MUCH MORE OF THIS.
IT REALLY MISSES THE FOOD
I USED TO PUT IN IT.
- ( stomach growling )
- SASAMI, IF I HAD ANY MONEY,
I'D PAY YOU TO COOK.
- IN MY WILDEST DREAMS
I NEVER THOUGHT
WE'D STARVE TO DEATH ON A PLANET
WITH SO MUCH FOOD ALL AROUND.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT.
WE WOULDN'T HAVE
TO GO THROUGH THIS
IF YOU HADN'T TRIED TO GRAB
ALL OF SASAMI'S MONEY.
- AND I WOULD HAVE
GOT IT,
IF YOUR HAND HADN'T BEEN
THERE BEFORE ME.
- ( stomach growling )
- NEVER MIND.
I'M TOO WEAK TO FIGHT.
- DON'T WORRY, EVERYONE.
DUE TO THE CURRENT EMERGENCY,
I VOLUNTEER TO COOK
SOMETHING FOR YOU.
- NO WAY.
THAT'S A RECIPE FOR DISASTER.
IF YOU SET FOOT IN THERE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BREAK THE FAUCET,
CHOP THE CUTTING BOARD
IN HALF,
SMASH ALL THE PLATES
AND GLASSES,
INCINERATE THE POTS AND
SOMEHOW CAUSE A GAS EXPLOSION.
- WHAT A HORRIBLE THING
TO SAY.
ARE YOU IMPLYING
THAT I'M INCOMPETENT?
- ( all groaning )
- ( Ryoko laughs )
- HUH?
- OH.
- SOMETHING SMELLS YUMMY, AND
IT'S COMING FROM THE KITCHEN.
- YES, BUT WHO'S
IN THERE?
NOBODY AROUND HERE
KNOWS HOW TO COOK.
- ( all mumbling )
- TIME FOR DINNER.
- WASHU, YOU SAVED
OUR LIVES.
- WHAT DID YOU MAKE
FOR US?
IT SMELLS SO RICH,
CREAMY AND DREAMY.
- YOU DIDN'T HAPPEN
TO BREAK ANY DISHES
WHILE YOU WERE IN THERE
COOKING, DID YOU?
- NOT EVERYONE'S
A BUTTER-FINGERS.
I HAVE TO ADMIT,
WASHU,
I HAD NO IDEA
YOU KNEW HOW TO COOK.
- BOTTOM LINE,
I CAN'T BOIL WATER.
- HUH?
- TOO MUCH WORK.
HOWEVER, I CAN DUPLICATE
THE COOKING PROCESS
BY MANIPULATING
A DNA SEQUENCE.
HUH?
- UGH.
- I GUARANTEE
IT'LL BE DELICIOUS.
WHO WANTS TO BE
THE FIRST ONE TO DIG IN?
- ARGH!
( girls screaming )
- ( distant horns honking )
- YOU GONNA BUY IT?
- WHAT?
- THIS PIECE HERE.
- OH, I MIGHT WANT TO.
- MEOW.
- ( giggles )
WHAT A CUTE PET YOU HAVE.
HERE.
( giggles )
I'M YUGI.
- OH, HOW RUDE OF ME.
MY NAME'S SASAMI.
PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
- MEOW.
- I WOULDN'T FORGET YOU.
THIS IS RYO-OHKI.
- HI.
YOU'RE JUST PRECIOUS.
HOW ARE YOU?
- MEOW.
- Sasami: LOOK.
- ( both girls giggling )
- I THINK I'LL WEAR THIS
TO MY NEXT PARTY
AND SEE IF ANYBODY
NOTICES.
- ( both giggling )
- I'M SURE
YOU'LL LOVE THIS.
- LET ME ASK YOU
SOMETHING.
I JUST MET YOU,
BUT WE'RE FRIENDS, RIGHT?
- UH...
OF COURSE WE'RE FRIENDS.
- GOOD.
IN THAT CASE,
WHY DON'T YOU COME TO MY HOUSE
AND WE'LL PLAY?
- NOW?
WELL, I GUESS I COULD.
- HOORAY!
JUST FOLLOW ME.
- I'M AFRAID THERE'S NO EXIT
OVER THERE.
- OH, SURE THERE IS.
WATCH.
- OH?  OH.
- COME ON, SASAMI.
RIGHT THIS WAY.
HURRY.
- ALL RIGHT, FINE.
OH!
( gasps ) OH.
WHERE ARE WE?
- SASAMI!
( echoing )
COME ON, FOLLOW ME.
- YUGI, WAIT UP.
( screams )
WHERE ARE WE?
- I SEE YOU FINALLY WOKE UP.
- MEOW.
- OH, THERE YOU ARE.
- OF COURSE.
LET'S PLAY HERE, OKAY?
- OKAY.  BUT--
- BUT WHAT?
- I FEEL THERE'S SOMETHING
UNPLEASANT AROUND HERE.
- REALLY?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- A DEFINITE FEELING
OF SOMETHING EVIL.
- EVIL?
- I REALLY DON'T THINK
IT'S SAFE TO STAY HERE.
THERE MUST BE A WAY
OUT OF THIS PLACE.
COME ON,
LET'S FIND IT.
- ( panting )
- ( voice laughing )
- ( gasps )
WHO'S THERE?
- WHAT ARE YOU
PANICKING FOR?
THERE'S NOWHERE TO RUN.
HIYAH!
- WATCH OUT!
( whimpers )
- YOU'RE TRAPPED IN THE WORLD
INSIDE THE MIRROR.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL ACCEPT
THAT THERE'S NO ESCAPE.
- I REFUSE
TO BELIEVE THAT.
OH!
WE'VE GOT TO
MAKE A RUN FOR IT, YUGI.
HELP!
SOMEBODY HELP!
- HUH?
- MEOW!
- LEAVE US ALONE,
YOU BULLY.
- ( laughs )
HOW VERY IMPOLITE OF YOU.
YOU SAID
YOU WANTED TO PLAY.
- NOW I WANT TO GO.
- THAT'S QUITE IMPOSSIBLE.
IF YOU INSIST
ON LEAVING,
I'LL HAVE TO KILL YOU.
HIYAH!
- ( screams )
- MEOW!
MEOW!
- ARGH!
- ( meowing )
- THANKS FOR SAVING ME,
RYO-OHKI.
- THERE'S MORE.
- ( gasps )
- WATCH OUT, YUGI.
( screams )
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO BE HURT.
- UH...
- ( Tsugaru laughs )
YOU SHOULD LEARN
TO BEHAVE.
NOW, I'M AFRAID, YOU'LL HAVE TO
PAY THE ULTIMATE PENALTY.
WHA--?  WHAT'S THIS?
- ( meowing )
- WHO ARE YOU?
HEE-YAH!
- ( meowing )
MEOW, MEOW, MEOW!
- YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS.
- MEOW, MEOW, MEOW!
- NOW BLAST A PASSAGE
FOR US.
- MEOW.
- OPEN FIRE!
- MEOW, MEOW!
- ( both scream )
- OH.
- MEOW.
- YUGI, YOU MADE IT OUT?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
- ( gasps )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
SASAMI?
- MM-HMM.
- SASAMI!
- HUH?
- ( panting )
OH, I WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
I WAS LOOKING EVERYWHERE.
PLEASE DON'T EVER GO OFF
ON YOUR OWN LIKE THAT.
- I'M SORRY, TENCHI,
BUT I MET SOMEONE NEW.
SEE?  HERE SHE IS.
HER NAME'S YUGI, AND WE'VE
ALREADY BECOME GOOD FRIENDS.
- A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
- OH, HOW DO YOU DO?
- I SAVED THIS.
IT BELONGS TO YOU.
- OH.
THANK YOU.
I THOUGHT
IT WAS LOST FOREVER.
AWW.
- ( quiet tune playing )
- A MUSIC BOX IS NICE,
BUT KIND OF DEPRESSING.
NO MATTER HOW CHEERFUL
THE MUSIC IS AT THE BEGINNING,
YOU KNOW THAT EVENTUALLY
IT'S GOING TO WIND DOWN
AND STOP PLAYING.
- TENCHI, LET ME
ASK YOU AGAIN.
PLEASE BE MY BOYFRIEND.
I REALLY WANT YOU
TO GO STEADY WITH ME.
- LISTEN TO ME.
I'M SORRY,
I'M JUST NOT READY
FOR A RELATIONSHIP YET.
- YOU-- YOU DON'T LIKE ME?
- SAKUYA, PLEASE,
I DIDN'T MEAN TO--
- ( sobbing )
- TRY TO UNDERSTAND.
MM.
- BYE, SASAMI.
I'LL SEE YOU SOMETIME SOON.
- ( all moaning )
- ( stomach growling )
- Ryoko: I HAVEN'T EATEN
IN DAYS.
SOON I'LL BE NOTHING
BUT SKIN AND BONES.
- ( stomach growling )
- All: WHERE ARE YOU, SASAMI?
PLEASE COME BACK!
- ( upbeat song playing )
- MEOW, MEOW.
MEOW.
- I'M KIYONE,
FIRST-CLASS DETECTIVE
IN THE GALAXY POLICE.
WE'RE ALL EXCITED BECAUSE IT'S
TENCHI ANNIVERSARY TOMORROW,
THE MOST MEMORABLE DAY
OF OUR LIVES
WHEN WE FIRST
MET TENCHI.
TIME REALLY FLIES.
TWO YEARS HAVE ALREADY PASSED
SINCE THE DAY WE CRASH-LANDED
ON THE FACE OF EARTH.
THAT TURNED OUT TO BE
THE DAY OF MY DOOM.
YES, THAT WAS WHEN ALL MY
CAREER AMBITIONS
WERE CRASHED
TO PIECES.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF THE NEW
"TENCHI MUYO" SERIES,
"THE DAY WE MET."