- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- ( horns honking )
- ( sighs )
- ( ringing )
- WAH!
- ( groans )
( growls )
IT'S WASHU. WHO MAY I
ASK IS CALLING, PLEASE?
WHAT A SURPRISE, TENCHI.
- SORRY TO BOTHER YOU
SO LATE AT NIGHT.
I'M CALLING TO ASK
FOR A FAVOR.
- OH, I'M FLATTERED.
WHAT A NAUGHTY BOY YOU ARE.
I know how lonely it
must be there in Tokyo.
Sleeping in your little room.
I can be there in a few minutes.
But I do have to clean up first.
- NO, PLEASE, WAIT!
IT'S ABOUT
THE DIMENSIONAL TUNNEL.
I'M CALLING TO ASK
IF YOU WOULD REMOVE IT.
- HMM?  WHY DO YOU SUDDENLY
WANT ME TO TAKE IT OUT?
- IT'S OBVIOUS, ISN'T IT?
I'M A BACHELOR LIVING ON MY OWN.
PEOPLE WILL TALK IF GIRLS
KEEP POPPING OUT OF NOWHERE
MORNING, NOON AND NIGHT.
- I SUPPOSE YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'LL TAKE IT OUT,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
IS IT A LOT OF TROUBLE?
- NOT REALLY. IN FACT, IT'LL BE
GONE BY THE TIME YOU WAKE UP.
- I APPRECIATE IT.
GOOD NIGHT.
- HMM...
- ( alarm beeping )
- HMM?
- ( sighs )
- ( meows )
- HUH?
- OH...
- ( snoring )
- ( chopping )
- ( sizzling )
- ( yawning )
- ( giggles )
- ( snoring )
- OKAY, EVERYONE, I'M PACKED.
ARE YOU READY TO GO?
- MISO SOUP, HOT IN THE POT!
- PICKLES AND SALMON,
I'M READY FOR JAMMIN'!
- LET'S MOVE,
I'M IN THE GROOVE!
- MEOW MEOW MEOW!
- DIMENSIONAL TUNNEL'S
IN PLACE.
LET'S GO VISIT TENCHI
IN TOKYO.
- All: YEAH!
- ( all cheer )
- ( all groan )
- OW!
- IT HURTS!
- WHO PUT THAT CEILING UP THERE?
- I THINK SOMETHING'S WRONG
WITH THE TUNNEL.
- WHAT?
- All: OHH...
- MISS WASHU?
- WE HAVE AN EMERGENCY!
SOMEONE BROKE THE TUNNEL!
- NO, SASAMI, I SHUT IT DOWN.
- ( both gasp )
- I BEG YOUR PARDON?
- WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO MEAN TO US?
IS IT BECAUSE I ATE THAT LAST
PIECE OF BLUEBERRY CHEESECAKE
YOU HAD HIDDEN IN
THE BACK OF THE REFRIGERATOR?
OR IS IT BECAUSE I PUT ON
THAT NURSE'S UNIFORM
YOU LIKE TO WEAR
AND RIPPED THE PANTS LAST WEEK
WHEN YOU WERE OUT OF THE HOUSE?
- HUH?
- OR IS IT 'CAUSE
I ACCIDENTLY POURED TEQUILA
ON YOUR COMPUTER
AND IT GOT DRUNK,
AND THREW UP SQUARE ROOTS?
YOU DID THAT?
YOU CLOSED THE TUNNEL
FOR SUCH TRIVIAL REASONS?
- OH, PUT A LID ON IT.
LOOK, IF YOU MUST KNOW,
TENCHI CALLED ME LAST NIGHT
AND ASKED ME IF I'D PLEASE
REMOVE IT.
- YOU MUST BE MISTAKEN.
- HE WAS PROBABLY JOKING.
- HE COULDN'T HAVE BEEN SERIOUS.
THE TUNNEL IS THE BOND THAT
CONNECTS US TO HIM IN TOKYO.
- ( stomach grumbles loudly )
- SORRY, EVERYONE!
I GUESS I'M HUNGRIER
THAN I REALIZED.
- WE'RE HAVING
AN EMERGENCY HERE.
PUT YOUR STOMACH ON HOLD.
OH, WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHY IN THE WORLD
TENCHI WON'T LET US BRING HIM
HIS BREAKFAST.
( gasps ) GOOD HEAVENS!
HE COULD BE SICK,
AND DESPERATELY NEED OUR HELP!
WE HAVE TO GET TO TENCHI'S ROOM
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
IT'S LIFE AND DEATH!
PUT THE DIMENSIONAL TUNNEL
BACK IN PLACE RIGHT NOW!
- THERE IS NO PROBLEM.
HE'S NOT SICK.
- WOULD YOU LIKE A CUP OF TEA?
- THANKS.
OOH.
- WHAT'S UP?
- I WAS THINKING HOW
PLEASANT IT IS TO FINALLY
HAVE A QUIET MEAL.
- UH...
- YEAH, WHAT IS IT?
- HUH?  MM-MM.
I SPACED OUT.
- HEY!  TENCHI!
ARE YOU READY?
WE HAVE TO GET TO SCHOOL, RIGHT?
( giggles )
- OH, NO, I DIDN'T SEE
WHAT TIME IT WAS.
- SAKUYA, I HAVE TO GO.
- UH...
MM.
- ( snoring )
( mumbles )
TENCHI...
LET ME RUB YOUR FEET.
- ( clears throat )
- I FIGURE, IF WE WANT
TO KNOW THE TRUTH,
WE'LL HAVE TO GO ASK TENCHI.
- GEE, HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO THAT?
- WITH THE TUNNEL DOWN,
WE'LL HAVE TO BUY A TICKET
AND GO TO TOKYO.
- PLEASE, WE'RE ALREADY
IN THE RED THIS MONTH.
THERE'S NO EXTRA MONEY
FOR THAT.
- I FIGURED AS MUCH.
I THINK THE PERSON WHO'S
RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS MESS
SHOULD STEP FORWARD
AND PAY OUR WAY.
- EH?  NOW WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
IT'S MY FAULT?
- OF COURSE IT IS.
IF YOU AREN'T RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS SITUATION,
I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW
WHO IS.
- I WAS SIMPLY TRYING TO DO
THE THING THAT WAS BEST FOR HIM.
- REALLY?!  WELL, IT'S OBVIOUS
YOU HAVEN'T GIVEN A THOUGHT
TO WHAT'D BE BEST FOR US.
- UH.  WELL, NO,
THAT'S NOT WHAT I WAS SAYING.
- THEN YOU SHOULD GIVE US
THE MONEY TO TRAVEL TO TOKYO.
- ( meows angrily )
- ( all sobbing )
- ( chuckles nervously )
I WOULD IF I COULD,
BUT I CAN'T REALLY AFFORD TO
ON MY TINY SALARY.
- I DON'T THINK
THAT'S QUITE TRUE.
- ( gasps )
- HERE!
LET ME DEMONSTRATE.
OKAY, THIS BLOCK REPRESENTS
THE TOTAL AMOUNT OF
FATHER'S MONTHLY SALARY.
FROM THAT, WE TAKE AWAY TAXES
AND BASIC LIVING EXPENSES.
THEN FROM THE BALANCE OF THAT,
WE TAKE AWAY THE COST OF DRINKS,
CIGARETTES AND THE NEWSPAPER
HE READS EVERY DAY.
THEN WE TAKE AWAY
ALL HIS COMIC BOOKS
AND ALL THE CANDY
BARS HE HAS HIDDEN
IN EVERY SINGLE ROOM
OF THE HOUSE...
AND THAT'S WHAT'S LEFT.
- Both: HMM?
- THEN, YOU MULTIPLY
THIS FIGURE BY 12,
AND THEN YOU MULTIPLY IT
AGAIN BY THE NUMBER OF YEARS
HE'S BEEN EARNING HIS SALARY.
- OH.  YEAH.
- THAT'S THE AMOUNT HE'S SAVED
ALL THESE YEARS.
AND IT'S ENOUGH TO SEND
FIVE ADULTS,
ONE CHILD AND ONE PET ON
A ROUND-TRIP BUS RIDE TO TOKYO.
WITH ENOUGH LEFT OVER FOR
SOME BOXED LUNCHES AND SNACKS.
PLUS A LITTLE SPENDING MONEY!
NOW, ANY QUESTIONS?
- ( giggles )
I SEE WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
IT'S LOGICAL.
- I KNEW HE HAD THE MONEY
TO PAY FOR THIS TRIP ALL ALONG.
- WELL, WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
LET'S SEARCH THE HOUSE.
- GOOD!  WE CAN GO SEE
TENCHI AFTER ALL.
- ( meowing )
- THANK GOODNESS
YOU FIGURED IT OUT, WASHU.
I WAS GETTING DISAPPOINTED.
- ( sobbing )
THERE GOES MY SECRET SAVINGS!
- ( groans )
- ( indistinct chatter )
- HEY, TENCHI, DID
YOU SEE THAT WOMEN'S
PRO WRESTLING MATCH YESTERDAY?
SADAKO WAS WILD!
- SAKUYA!
GOOD MORNING.
- HI. NOW ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS BUY SOME
INGREDIENTS, RIGHT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.  HMM?
NOW I HEARD
THAT YOU GOT SAKUYA
TO PACK YOU A LUNCH TODAY,
TENCHI.
- MAYBE I DID.
- WELL?
- WELL, WHAT?
- OH...
COME ON!
- AAH!
- WELL, DID YOU FINALLY TELL HER
YOU WERE IN LOVE WITH HER?
- WHAT?  NO WAY.
- OHH.  I SUPPOSE
THERE'S STILL TIME TOMORROW.
- ARE YOU NUTS? TOMORROW'S THE
DAY OF THE SCHOOL FESTIVAL.
- I KNOW THAT!
I DON'T MEAN DURING IT, SILLY.
YOU KNOW THE LEGEND--
ANYONE WHO DECLARES THEIR LOVE
AT THE PARTY
FOLLOWING THE FESTIVAL
CAN EXPECT TO LIVE
HAPPILY EVER AFTER.
- OH.
- Sakuya: IS THAT TRUE?
- YOU BET.
- ANYTIME DURING THE PARTY.
- MM-HMM.
- TENCHI...
- AAH!
- ...WHY DON'T YOU COME
WITH ME AFTER SCHOOL
TO WATCH THE GIRLS'
WRESTLING TEAM?
THEY'RE HAVING
A MAJOR PRACTICE TODAY.
- ( laughs )
VERY SOON...
THE TWO STARS WILL OVERLAP.
THEN IT WILL BE TIME.
- HMM?  WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- WHAT?  NOTHING.
- ( Sugano's voice )  ANYONE WHO
DECLARES THEIR LOVE AT THE PARTY
FOLLOWING THE FESTIVAL,
CAN EXPECT TO LIVE
HAPPILY EVER AFTER.
- MAKE SURE THAT MAT IS TIGHT.
- OKAY!
- TIE IT OFF IN THE CORNER!
- GIVE ME SOME SLACK.
- OH, YUCK,
LOOK AT THIS DIRTY OLD THING.
- IT MUST HAVE BELONGED
TO SOMEONE WHO GRADUATED.
- JUST THROW IT AWAY.
- I THINK WE SHOULD BURN IT.
- I BROUGHT THE CREPE COOKER.
- THANKS.
WE'RE REALLY GONNA NEED IT.
- CAN YOU DO US A FAVOR, PLEASE,
AND SET IT UP FOR US?
- OH, YEAH, SURE.
- I CAN HELP.
- OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
I HAVE A MEETING WITH
THE MEMBERS OF THE
FESTIVAL COMMITTEE.
I'LL BE GONE FOR AWHILE.
- DON'T WORRY, WE'LL BE FINE.
- Both: HMM?  OH!
- I'M GOING TO FIND
SOMETHING TO EAT.
MY STOMACH JUST REMINDED
ME I'VE BEEN IGNORING IT
ALL MORNING.
- I'M GONNA TAKE A QUICK BREAK,
AND SEE IF I CAN FIND
SOME MASKING TAPE.
- WE'LL BE HERE
WHEN YOU GET BACK.
- UH, YOU HAVE A SCREWDRIVER?
- OH, SURE.
- WHAT A COWARD. WE'RE GIVING
HIM EVERY OPPORTUNITY.
- GO FOR IT.
COME ON, TENCHI.
- I THINK HE NEEDS A KICK
IN THE PANTS TO GET MOVING.
I MIGHT NEED SOME
HELP WITH THIS.
ALL RIGHT.
I THINK WE'RE GONNA SEE
SOME SPARKS, GIRLS.
( all gasp )
- TENCHI!
WHY ARE YOU WASTING
YOUR TIME HERE?
LET'S WATCH THE FEMALE
WRESTLING TEAM WORK OUT.
- All:
HE'S MESSING UP EVERYTHING.
- ( silently )
- HE'S CERTAINLY
MESSING UP MY PLANS.
TIME FOR A DISTRACTION.
OFF YOU GO.
- HIYAH!  HIYAH!  HIYAH!  HA!
HA!  HIYAH!
- EVERYBODY'S TOO BUSY
TO GO WITH ME TO THE PRACTICE.
- I NEED THAT NUT.
- HUH?
- UH... OH!
- ALLOW ME.
I'M AVAILABLE IF YOU NEED HELP.
- ( bell rings )
- AAH!
HUH?
HUH?  WHOA!
- GERMAN SUPLEX!
- WHOA!
- HUH?
- UH...
- WHERE'S AMAGASAKI?
- ( squeaks )
- WHOA!
THIS FEELS GREAT.
MY GOODNESS, IT'S ALMOST
LIKE I'M FLYING.
- ( yawns )
- I GUESS I MUST HAVE
OVERSLEPT A LITTLE.
WHAT'S HAPPENED DOWN THERE?!
- ( muffled groaning )
- SPEAK UP, I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
- ( muffled speech )
- IT WAS A GANG OF ROBBERS,
WASN'T IT?
- UH, WELL, NO, I WOULDN'T
SAY THAT EXACTLY.
- I CAN'T FIND A SIGN
OF IT ANYWHERE.
- ME EITHER, AND I CHECKED
EVERY ROOM IN THE HOUSE.
- MAYBE THERE'S A HIDDEN SAFE
IN THE WALL.
RYOKO, I SEE YOU
FINALLY WOKE UP.
- WHAT ARE BUMBLE BRAINS UP TO?
SO, YOU'VE BEEN SEARCHING
FOR HIS SECRET STASH, HUH?
- THAT'S RIGHT, AND NOW
THAT YOU'RE AWAKE,
YOU CAN SEARCH WITH US.
WE CAN USE THE EXTRA HELP.
- I'M NOT GONNA HELP YOU.
- WHY NOT?
- BECAUSE I'M BONDED
TO TENCHI BY TRUE LOVE
NO MATTER WHAT
THE DISTANCE.
AND ANYWAY, I CAN FLY THERE
WHENEVER I WANT.
- RYOKO, YOU CHEATER!
I WON'T LET HER
GET AWAY WITH THIS.
FINE.  WE DON'T NEED HER.
WE'LL FIND THE MONEY ON OUR OWN.
- AAH!  I'M GONNA BE ROBBED!
HELP!
- WE'RE BACK.
- WE'RE ALL DONE.
- I SET UP THE CREPE COOKER.
IT'S READY TO GO.
- THANK YOU.
- PERFECT.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS
LOAD UP THE SUPPLIES
FOR TOMORROW.
- SAKUYA, CAN YOU BUY
THE INGREDIENTS WE'LL
NEED TO MAKE THE CREPES?
- SURE, NO PROBLEM.
- YOU'LL NEED SOME HELP.
TENCHI, CAN YOU GO ALONG
AND GIVE HER A HAND
BRINGING EVERYTHING BACK?
- NO PROBLEM.
I'LL BE GLAD TO.
- THANKS.
- Girls:
HAVE A NICE TIME!
- IS THAT BAG
TOO HEAVY FOR YOU?
- NO, I'M OKAY.
IT'S SO WEIRD.
- WHAT?
- THE GIRLS, HAVEN'T THEY
BEEN ACTING STRANGE?
- NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
IT SEEMS LIKE THEY'VE BEEN
DOING EVERYTHING
THEY CAN COME UP WITH
JUST TO MAKE SURE
YOU AND I END UP ALONE.
- EXACTLY WHAT
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THE FACT IS, I KINDA LIKE
BEING ALONE WITH YOU.
- HEY!  TENCHI!
- HUH?
- HI!
- MM?
- ( bell rings )
- AAH.  NOT AGAIN.
- AX BOMBER!
- WH-- WHY ME?!
- UH-- I- HUH?
- ( girls sighing, groaning )
- I GUESS THE MONEY'S HIDDEN
SOMEPLACE ELSE.
- I DON'T CARE ANYMORE.
I'M TRIED OF LOOKING FOR IT.
- ( weakly )
MEOW MEOW MEOW.
- I'M TIRED TOO.
I THINK IT'S TIME TO GIVE UP.
- WE CAN'T BE DEFEATED
LIKE THIS!
AFTER ALL, WE'RE GALAXY
POLICE DETECTIVES.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO WASHU?
SHE JUST DISAPPEARED.
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
- SHE HASN'T BEEN AROUND
FOR A COUPLE OF HOURS.
- I'M HERE.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT?!  GOOD HEAVENS.
- HUH?
- OH.
- AAH.
- MISS WASHU,
WHAT IS THAT THING?
- MEOW MEOW MEOW.
- GLAD YOU ASKED.
THIS, MY FRIENDS,
IS AN AUTOMATIC SELF-PROPELLED
TREASURE-FINDING CANINE ROBOT.
I CALL HIM FIDO.
- ( barks )
- HE'S SO CUTE!
- YEAH, REAL CUTE.
- I'VE PROGRAMMED HIM
WITH SPECIAL ABILITIES
SO HE CAN FIND ANY KIND OF
TREASURE HIDDEN BY ANYONE,
ANYWHERE.
THE MONEY WILL BE OURS
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
- ( girls cheering )
- ( howls )
- Girls: AWW!
- HE LOOKS LIKE A MUTT.
- WELL, WE'VE GOT ALL
THE GROCERIES WE NEED.
- THAT'S GREAT.
YOUR NEXT ASSIGNMENT
IS TO TAKE THE STACK OF POSTERS
AND PUT THEM UP ON THE CAMPUS.
- OKAY.
- TENCHI, CAN YOU HELP HER OUT?
THEY'RE PRETTY HEAVY.
- OH, SURE.
- WAIT.
BEFORE YOU DO THAT,
YOU HAVE TO GO TO THE ROOF
AND HANG THESE BANNERS.
- Girls:
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
- DID YOU MAKE SURE
THE ROOF WAS CLEAR,
SO THEY'LL BE ALONE?
- YES, MA'AM.
THEY SHOULD HAVE THE
ROOF TO THEMSELVES
FOR AT LEAST A HALF-HOUR.
- IT'S A GREAT OPPORTUNITY.
I HOPE HE DOESN'T BLOW IT.
- COME ON, TENCHI, GO!
- DARN, I WONDER WHERE FATHER
COULD HAVE HIDDEN THAT MONEY.
OH, MY.
- ( cash register dings )
- WOW!  WHAT A LUCKY BREAK!
I CAN BUY AT LEAST SEVEN
SEAWEED SNACKS WITH THIS.
- WOOF!
- HUH?!
HI...
- ( barks )
- ( laughs )
COME HERE, FIDO.
LET ME HAVE A LITTLE
TALK WITH YOU.
- I HAVE NEVER BEEN BEATEN
BY ANYONE.
BUT I WISH I COULD MEET
A WRESTLER
WHO WOULD CHALLENGE ME
AS AN EQUAL.
IN ALL MY ENCOUNTERS,
I HAVE FOLLOWED THE CODE
OF A TRUE PROFESSIONAL.
I HAVE GIVEN NO MERCY,
AND I HAVE EXPECTED NONE
FROM MY OPPONENTS.
NOW, WHAT IS LEFT TO FIRE
MY COMPETITIVE SPIRIT?
- ( gasps )
- TENCHI, WHERE ARE YOU HIDING?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT MAN
IS ABLE TO WALK AROUND
AFTER I PUT MY BEST MOVES
ON HIM.
COULD HE BE THE ONE WHO
REKINDLES MY COMPETITIVE FIRE?
- SOMETHING IS GOING ON.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS,
BUT MY BLOOD IS BOILING.
IT'S WEIRD!
I COULD FEEL IT TAKING OVER,
TURNING ME INTO AN ANIMAL!
I BETTER GO
AND TELL TENCHI.
TENCHI!
- ( bell rings )
- ELBOW CRASH!
- ( screams )
I KNOW YOU'RE IN HERE, TENCHI.
HELLO?
- ( bell rings )
- BRAIN BUSTER!
- WHOA!
TENCHI, I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
- ( bell rings )
- FLYING CROSS TOP!
- WAH-HA!
( weakly )
HELLO, TENCHI?
- ( bell rings )
- ( moans )
- GIANT SWING!
- NOT AGAIN!
- ( bird squawking )
- ( sighing, groaning )
( chuckles )
I'M FIGHTING AN INVISIBLE ENEMY,
BUT I'M READY FOR HIM.
MY SENSES ARE REALLY TINGLING.
I NEVER FELT SO ALIVE.
( laughs maniacally )
WHOEVER YOU ARE,
I'M READY FOR YOU!
WATCH THIS, TENCHI!
- ( bell rings )
- I KNEW YOU WOULD COME!
IT'S THE FINAL SHOWDOWN.
- AAH!
( grunts )
- DROP KICK!
- ( grunts )
( groans )
- GET UP AND FIGHT,
AMAGASAKI!
- I'M GETTING BEAT UP HERE,
TENCHI.
- GET UP, AMAGASAKI,
GET UP.
- IT ALMOST SOUNDS
LIKE THEY'RE CHEERING FOR ME.
- ( crowd cheering )
- SHOW 'EM WHAT YOU'RE
MADE OF, BUDDY!
- ( groans loudly )
( panting )
- YAH!
- MM.
- HA!
- WHOA!
( grunts )
( screaming )
- WAH!
- ( groans )
- OH!
( thinking)
HE SIZED UP MY ATTACK.
AND CAME BACK
WITH ONE OF HIS OWN.
- GOTCHA!
- ( chuckles )
( groaning )
- IT'S OVER NOW.
YOU HAVE TO ACCEPT DEFEAT.
- YOU MAY CALL IT A DEFEAT,
BUT I CALL IT A VICTORY.
- HUH?
- MM.
- AAH!  WHOA!
- HUH?  AAH!
- AAH!
- ( both grunt )
- ( gasp )
- ( groans loudly )
WHOA!
- YAH!
DON'T JUMP
TO CONCLUSIONS NOW.
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
- ( laughs )
I SAW NOTHING.
YOUR SECRET'S SAFE WITH ME.
I MEAN, IT WAS JUST
A LITTLE KISS, WASN'T IT?
DON'T YOU WORRY.
I DON'T PLAN TO TELL ANYBODY.
I SWEAR.
I'M A SENSITIVE GUY.
- AMAGASAKI!
YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG.
- HUH?
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE!
THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
THIS IS THE MASK
OF THE FAMOUS FEMALE WRESTLER,
IKARINU SADAKO.
SHE MUST HAVE BEEN
MY OPPONENT ALL ALONG,
AND I DEFEATED HER.
ALL RIGHT!
- PRINCESS, HAVE YOU
BY CHANCE
FOUND MY SECRET
SAVINGS YET?
- SO FAR WE'VE HAD NO LUCK.
- OH, GOOD ANSWER.
THAT'S JUST FINE.
- ( chuckles )
( laughs )
- ( classical music playing )
- TOMORROW.
- ANYONE WHO DECLARES
THEIR LOVE AT THE PARTY
FOLLOWING THE FESTIVAL
CAN EXPECT TO LIVE
HAPPILY EVER AFTER.
- TOMORROW IS THE DAY
WHEN IT ALL BEGINS
TO DISINTEGRATE.
- ( upbeat music playing )
- ( people singing in Japanese )
- YEAH!
( growls )
MEOW.
- HI, THERE,
I'M RYOKO.
HEY, TENCHI, YOU WON'T BE FOOLED
BY THAT SAKUYA BABE, WILL YOU?
AYEKA AND EVERYONE
GOT WORRIED
AND WENT TO CHECK ON YOU.
BUT I'M NOT ONE OF THEM,
'CAUSE I TRUST YOU COMPLETELY.
OH, TENCHI.
I KNOW THINGS COULD BE BUSY
WITH THE SCHOOL FESTIVAL
AND ALL THAT, BUT, WELL...
I STILL HOPE YOU FIND TIME
TO HAVE ANOTHER DATE
WITH ME AGAIN.
JUST THE TWO OF US.
( giggles )
THE NEXT EPISODE OF
THE NEW TENCHI MUYO SERIES...