- ( theme song playing )
- IT'S AMAZING!
I'VE BEEN SO INCREDIBLY DENSE.
( laughs )
I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO CLOSE UP THE DIMENSIONAL
TUNNEL FOR SO LONG,
AND NOW I KNOW.
- ( birds chirping )
- ( giggles )
IF I'M VERY QUIET, I CAN SNEAK
THROUGH THE DIMENSIONAL TUNNEL
TO SEE TENCHI.
- I JUST HAVE TO FOLD
THIS COMFORTER,
AND THE TUNNEL
IS CLOSED.
I'LL HAVE
SOME PEACE!
- ( music playing )
- NO MORE CHAOS AND HAVOC
AND NOISE AND UNPREDICTABLE
MOOD SWINGS.
I'LL GO BACK TO BEING
JUST A KID,
HAPPY WITHOUT
THESE WOMEN.
- IT'S THE PERFECT TIME
TO BE ALONE WITH TENCHI
WHILE EVERYONE ELSE
IS SLEEPING.
IT WILL BE SO ROMANTIC,
JUST A NICE,
OLD-FASHIONED GIRL LIKE
MYSELF, ALONE WITH HER MAN.
( laughs )
IMAGINE THE POSSIBILITIES
FOR TWO PEOPLE
SO VERY MUCH IN LOVE
WITH EACH OTHER.
PREPARE FOR BLISS!
STRANGE.  SOMEONE MUST HAVE
ACCIDENTALLY
BLOCKED OFF THE ENTRANCE
TO THE TUNNEL.
SEVERAL MEASLY LAYERS
OF CONCRETE AND WOOD
AREN'T GONNA KEEP ME
FROM MY LOVE.
MY HEAD'S MUCH TOO HARD
FOR THAT.
HA!
- ( grunts )
EARTHQUAKE!
TAKE COVER!
OOPS.
- Ryoko: MY LOVE.
- ARGH!
- OUCH.
OH, HE'S UNCONSCIOUS.
OH, MINOR HEAD TRAUMA'S
A SMALL PRICE TO PAY
TO FINALLY BE
TOGETHER.
- YOU'RE SQUEEZING ME
REALLY HARD, RYOKO.
- OH, POOR LITTLE GUY.
YOU MUST BE
IN SO MUCH PAIN NOW.
WHY DON'T YOU LIE DOWN IN BED
WITH RYOKO, TENCHI?
I'LL HEAL YOU
WITH THE POWER OF LOVE.
( giggles )
- ( Tenchi grunting )
- OH, SO YOU LIKE
TO PLAY ROUGH, DO YOU?
OOH, YOU'RE A FEISTY ONE.
- HELP!
- LOOK!
- HUH?
- THE BRIGHTEST STAR.
IT'S THE SUN,
BURNING HOT AND INFERNAL
DAY AFTER DAY
FOR ALL OF ETERNITY.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?  OUR LOVE
COULD BE STRONGER THAN THE SUN.
- ( screaming )
- OH, TENCHI, I KNEW
YOU CARED ABOUT ME,
THAT I WAS THE ONLY
WOMAN FOR YOU.
THIS IS SO ROMANTIC.
- HELP!
- YOU KNOW,
YOU COULD USE
A FEW POINTERS
ON HOW TO MAKE A GIRL
FEEL APPRECIATED.
( grunts )
HEY, I'M A LADY.
BE GENTLE.
PUT ME DOWN.
- ( Tenchi grunts )
- HEY, WAIT.
- ( Ryoko screams )
HEY, WHAT'S
THE BIG IDEA?
- STAY HERE.  AND DON'T GO
SNEAKING BACK OVER TO TOKYO.
I CANNOT TAKE THIS ANYMORE,
RYOKO.  THAT'S IT.
DON'T COME TO TOKYO
TILL I SAY.
YOU GOT IT?
- TENCHI, COME BACK.
WHY ARE YOU ANGRY,
MY LOVER?
DID I SHOCK YOU
OR SAY SOMETHING WRONG
IN A FIT OF PASSION?
- Ayeka: HEY!
- HMM?
- YOU'VE WOKEN UP
EVERYONE IN THE HOUSE
WITH YOUR COMMOTION,
RYOKO.
- YEAH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
UP THERE ANYWAY, RYOKO?
- I WAS KIND OF HARD
ON HER,
BUT SHE HAS TO LEARN
THE MEANING OF "NO."
OH, LOOK WHAT TIME IT IS.
OH, I'M LATE.
- HMM, IT SEEMS THAT WHEN
TENCHI FOLDS HIS COMFORTER,
IT CREATES A STRONG BARRIER
BLOCKING THE TUNNEL.
THERE'S NO WAY
WE CAN OPEN IT.
- HOW CAN YOU STAY SO CALM
WHEN THE TUNNEL'S BLOCKED?
DON'T YOU REALIZE
THIS MEANS
THAT WE CAN'T SEE TENCHI
WHENEVER WE WANT TO?
- WELL, THERE'S NOTHING
WE CAN DO ABOUT IT.
- WE KNOW
WHOSE FAULT THIS IS.
OH, BECAUSE OF YOUR
STUPIDITY
TENCHI'S PUNISHING
ALL OF US.
- ( whimpering )
- OH, MY TENCHI,
THIS GULF THAT LIES
BETWEEN US--
PARTING IS SUCH
SWEET SORROW.
( sobbing )
- Ryoko: WASHU.
- HMM?
- CAN'T YOU COME UP WITH SOME
SCIENTIFIC WAY TO FIX THIS?
- ABSOLUTELY NOT.
HE HAS TO OPEN THE DIMENSIONAL
TUNNEL FROM HIS END
FOR IT TO BE
AT ALL ACCESSIBLE TO US.
HMM?
- IS THAT RIGHT?
THAT IS NOT
THE RIGHT ANSWER, WASHU.
NOW TELL ME YOU CAN DO
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS.
- OH, OKAY, RYOKO.
I'M SURE I COULD
FIGURE SOMETHING OUT.
- ( panting )
- MAN, YOU WORK HARD,
TENCHI.
HOW LONG
HAVE YOU BEEN HERE?
- NOT TOO LONG.
I WAS LATE.
- MY FATHER'S QUITE PLEASED
YOU'RE HERE.  ACTUALLY SO AM I.
OTHERWISE I'D BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR MAINTAINING THE SHRINE.
BUT I GUESS
IT'S QUITE AN HONOR
FOR YOU TO GET THE OPPORTUNITY
TO DO ALL THIS WORK.
- LUCKY GUY, I GUESS.
- WELL, TRY NOT TO BE
TOO LATE FOR SCHOOL.
- OH, NO, I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I'M RUNNING LATE ALREADY?
- ( clock chiming )
- ( panting )
IF I CAN HOLD THIS PACE, I'LL
MAKE IT JUST BEFORE THE BELL.
- Boy: HEY, TENCHI.
- HI.
- REPORTING, REPORTING.
TRANSMISSION HAS BEEN
RECEIVED.
- LOOK, WE HAVE
A TRANSMISSION.
- WOW, NOW WE CAN
REALLY SEE HIM.
- OH, TENCHI.
- OH, THERE YOU ARE, MY LOVE.
- MY REPORT DEVICE WILL
FOLLOW TENCHI AROUND ALL DAY
SO YOU CAN SEE
WHAT HE'S UP TO.
I SUSPECT THE ENTIRE FUTURE
OF ESPIONAGE
WILL BE ALTERED
BY MY INVENTION.
- THAT'S COOL, WASHU.
- MY TENCHI.
- MY MAN.
- I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW THIS VISUAL IMAGERY
GETS TRANSMITTED FROM TOKYO
ALL THE WAY TO OKAYAMA.
- ( beeps )
- TOKYO TRANSMISSION:
TENCHI CONVERSES
WITH A FRIEND AT SCHOOL.
- ( beep )
- SHIZUOKA TRANSMISSION:
TENCHI CONVERSES
WITH A FRIEND AT SCHOOL.
- ( beeps )
- NAGOYA TRANSMISSION:
TENCHI CONVERSES
WITH A FRIEND AT SCHOOL.
- ( beep )
- KYOTO TRANSMISSION:
TENCHI CONVERSES
WITH A FRIEND AT SCHOOL.
- ( beep )
- OSAKA TRANSMISSION:
TENCHI CONVERSES
WITH A FRIEND AT SCHOOL.
- ( beep )
- KOBE TRANSMISSION:
TENCHI CONVERSES
WITH A FRIEND AT SCHOOL.
- ( beep )
- HOME TRANSMISSION:
TENCHI CONVERSES
WITH A FRIEND AT SCHOOL.
- IT'S GREAT, HUH?
I'VE SENT OUT DOZENS
OF REPORT DEVICES
TO TRANSMIT
THIS INFORMATION.
IT'S FOOLPROOF, EXCEPT FOR
THE SLIGHT TIME LAG.
IT'S ALL REALLY
QUITE FASCINATING.
DON'T YOU THINK SO,
GUYS?
HMM.
I DON'T SUPPOSE
ANY OF YOU LISTENED
TO A SINGLE WORD
THAT I SAID.
- TENCHI.
- MY SWEETIE PIE.
- ALL THEY EVER WANT
TO KNOW
IS WHAT TENCHI'S DOING
EVERY SINGLE MINUTE.
- YEAH, NO KIDDING.
( sighs )
- IT'S SO NICE TO SEE EVERYONE
PAYING SUCH CLOSE ATTENTION
TO THE MATERIAL.
- ( students laughing )
- ( giggling )
- ( gasps )
- Tenchi: ARGH!
- Sasami: WOW,
SCHOOL'S DANGEROUS.
- ( laughing )
- ( whimpering )
- Sasami: I DON'T THINK WE'RE
SUPPOSED TO BE SEEING THIS.
- ( giggles )
- HEY!  OH.
- ( slurping )
- YOU'RE BOTH BECOMING
COUCH POTATOES
WITHOUT ANY MANNERS.
- ( exclaiming )
- IT'S THAT GIRL AGAIN.
- LOOK AT HER FLIRT
WITH HIM.
SOME WOMEN
ARE SO DESPERATE.
( grunts )
OUR TENCHI WOULD NEVER
FALL FOR A GIRL
SO AGGRESSIVE,
LIKE THAT SAKUYA.
- EVERY TIME WE LOOK,
THERE SHE IS.
AND WE'RE
STUCK HERE.
- THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME WAY
FOR ME TO BE WITH TENCHI.
I JUST HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT HOW.
- ( Yugi laughing )
THEY'RE REALLY
SO AMUSING TO WATCH,
CLOWNING AROUND
LIKE THAT.
BUT I CAN'T JUST LET THEM
SPY ON PEOPLE LIKE THAT.
IT MUST STOP.
- ( train horn blows )
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU WANT TO BREAK UP?
IT'S JUST SO SUDDEN.
WHERE'S THIS COMING FROM?
I KNOW WE'RE FAR APART,
BUT WE TRULY LOVE EACH OTHER.
AT LEAST
I LOVE YOU.
HELLO?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU DON'T LOVE ME ANYMORE?
HOW'S THAT POSSIBLE?
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
HOW COOL I AM?
- ( phone clicks )
- ( dial tone )
- ( sobbing )
ONCE MY VOICE WAS ENOUGH TO MAKE
HER HEART START POUNDING
AND SHE WAS IMPRESSED BY MEN
WITH CELLULAR TELEPHONES.
( sobs )
I BOUGHT THIS PHONE
TO IMPRESS YOU, MY LOVE,
AND NOW YOU'RE USING IT
TO BREAK UP WITH ME.
( sobbing )
( babbling )
WHY?  WHY?
WAS IT MY HAIR
OR THE FACT THAT I'M WEARING
WHITE SHOES AFTER LABOR DAY?
WHY?
- ( laughs )
- HUMANS CANNOT ENDURE
THE TORMENTS OF
LONG-DISTANCE RELATIONSHIPS.
THEY INEVITABLY LEAD
TO HEARTACHES
AND STRESS
AND PREMATURE BALDING.
I HAVE SEEN IT
HAPPEN.
THIS NEW DECREE
SHALL TAKE EFFECT NOW,
THE DECREE BEING
THE FOLLOWING:
LONG-DISTANCE RELATIONSHIPS
ARE FORBIDDEN.
( grunts, laughs )
- Ryoko: HEY,
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
IS TENCHI CAUGHT
IN A WINDSTORM?
- NO, THAT'S INTERFERENCE.
THIS SHOULD BE
NO PROBLEM TO CLEAR UP.
HUH?  HOW COULD
THIS BE HAPPENING?
- Ayeka: WHAT?
- MY REPORT DEVICES ARE...
- WHAT, WASHU?
- ...FOOLING AROUND
INSTEAD OF WORKING
LIKE THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO.
SOMEONE ELSE
MUST HAVE INTERFERED,
BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT
PROGRAMMED TO SLACK.
- HUH?
- ( snoring )
- I FEEL SO ALIVE.
- HEY THERE, BABY.
YOU COME TO THIS SPOT OFTEN?
'CAUSE I DO.
I BET
YOU'RE AN AIR SIGN.
- THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
- WELL, THEN YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO
MAKE IT MAKE SENSE.
- DON'T RUSH ME.
I'M THINKING.
IF I COULD JUST
FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S INTERFERING
WITH THE SYSTEM.
- ( snoring )
I MUST DESTROY
LONG-DISTANCE LOVE.
- MEOW?
MEOW!
- MEOW, MEOW.
- ( thunder crashing )
- LONG-DISTANCE LOVE
IS FORBIDDEN.
( yells )
IT WILL NO LONGER BE A PLAGUE
TO ALL OF MANKIND.
BY THE POWER OF ALL THINGS
BIG AND PURPLE,
IT MUST END NOW!
- ( yells )
( growling )
- HI, MY LOVE.
YOU MISS ME?
( exclaims )
- HIYAH!
- THERE'S AN ORDER
COMING IN.
( yelling )
- MUST STOP
LONG-DISTANCE LOVE.
( screaming )
- LONG-DISTANCE RELATIONSHIPS
ARE EVIL.
THEY MUST BE STOPPED.
OOH!  AH!
THEY'RE EVIL!
- IT MUST BE STOPPED.
IT MUST BE STOPPED.
- Ryoko: CAN'T YOU WORK
ANY FASTER?
TENCHI WILL BE
OLD AND GRAY
BY THE TIME
YOU GET THIS FIXED.
- BUT THAT SHOULD HAVE
DONE IT.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- OHH!
- MEN AND WOMEN
SEPARATED BY DISTANCE
WILL NEVER AGAIN
COMMUNICATE.
I'LL SCRAMBLE ALL
THE LONG-DISTANCE CALLS.
YOUR MISSION,
MY FRIENDS,
IS TO DESTROY ALL
LONG-DISTANCE RELATIONSHIPS.
THEY MUST BE STOPPED.
- HEY, GUYS,
WHY AREN'T WE MOVING?
- SOMEONE'S BLOCKING
THE WAY.
- TENCHI'S MOVING A VERY LARGE
PIECE OF FURNITURE
UP THE STAIRS IN HIS SCHOOL.
- ( beeping )
- TENCHI HAS NOW BEGUN TO MOVE
THE STAIRS OF HIS SCHOOL
SO HE CAN CLIMB UP A VERY LARGE
PIECE OF FURNITURE.
- TENCHI'S CLIMBING
THE MOUNTAIN
TO FIND THE LAND
OF VERY LARGE FURNITURE.
I CAN'T IMAGINE WHY.
- TENCHI'S ON TOP OF
A MOUNTAIN, WONDERING WHY.
- TENCHI IS OFF WANDERING AROUND
SOME BIG MOUNTAINTOP,
PROBABLY COMMUNING WITH NATURE,
SOMETHING LAME LIKE THAT.
- TENCHI-- TENCHI IS ABOUT
TO BE PUSHED OVER A CLIFF
BY A COW
AND A HIPPOPOTAMUS.
AND THE FALL
WILL MAKE HIM LAME.
- A HIPPO AND A COW
ARE ABOUT TO PUSH TENCHI
OFF A CLIFF.
- ( girls exclaim )
- WHAT'S HE DOING
UP THERE?
- WHERE DID HE FIND A HIPPO
IN JAPAN?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S GOING ON.
- Boys: COME ON.  I'M OPEN.
GO, AMAGAZAKI, GO.
TENCHI.  COME ON.
- ( grunts )
- TENCHI IS IN THE CAGE
AND HAS JUST BLOCKED
A BULLET-LIKE SHOT
FROM HIS FRIEND.
NOW HE HOLDS
A SOCCER BALL.
- TENCHI HAD TO BE
RESTRAINED IN A CAGE
AND NOW HIS FRIENDS ARE SHOOTING
AT HIM WITH BALLS AND BULLETS.
- TENCHI HAS BECOME A VICIOUS
AND UNCONTROLLABLE WILD ANIMAL
AND HAS BEEN EXILED IN A CAGE
BY HIS GUN-TOTING FRIENDS.
- TENCHI'S BECOME
A VICIOUS ANIMAL,
SO HIS FRIENDS EXILED HIM
TO SOME ISLAND FOR CRIMINALS.
- TENCHI, HE'S BECOME
A MONSTER
AND HE'S BEING SHOT AT
IN AUSTRALIA.
- LET'S SEE, TENCHI HAS BECOME
A VICIOUS DEMON
AND HE'S SPENDING TIME
IN HELL.
AND EGGS ARE BEING
THROWN AT HIM NOW.
- ( beeping )
TENCHI HAS BECOME
THE EGG-HATING DEMON OF HELL.
- ( all scream )
- WASHU, ARE YOU JUST TRYING
TO MESS WITH MY MIND?
- NO, YOUR MIND REALLY
DOESN'T NEED MY HELP.
HERE WE GO.
- TENCHI FINDS TRUE LOVE
ON A DESERTED ISLAND.
- ( growls )
- WELL, THE SUNSET'S
KIND OF PRETTY.
- Ayeka: THIS IS
JUST TERRIBLE.
EACH PICTURE
IS WORSE THAN THE LAST.
( whimpering )
- Washu: LOUNGING
ON A SUNSET BEACH
WITH A GIRL--
THAT'S NOT SO BAD.
BUT I MUST ADMIT,
IT'S NOT LIKE TENCHI AT ALL.
- THIS IS YOUR FAULT.
- ( slurping )
- HMM?
DID YOU JUST HEAR
A STRANGE NOISE?
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- NEVER MIND.  IT'S MY
IMAGINATION.  GOTTA GO.
- HUH?
- I GUESS
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
- WELL, I'LL WALK
WITH YOU.
- THANKS.
- THAT WAS A GREAT SAVE
AT SOCCER TODAY.
- Sasami: WHA--
WHAT IS HE DOING?
- I'VE LOST HIM
FOREVER.
- ( gasps ) AYEKA?
DON'T LOSE IT.
THIS HAS GOT TO BE
SOME KIND OF MISTAKE.
- TENCHI, HOW COULD YOU
DO THIS TO ME?
YOU'RE SUCH A CRUEL MAN.
I LOVE YOU.
- I CAN'T EVEN HEAR
MY OWN THOUGHTS IN THIS ROOM.
- HMM?
- I'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
- ( panting )
- Sasami: WHAT IN THE WORLD?
- ( trumpets )
- AN ELEPHANT COSTUME--
THAT'S NICE.
- OH, MY DEAR TENCHI,
IF ONLY I UNDERSTOOD
WHY YOU WERE PRACTICING
CALLIGRAPHY
IN AN ELEPHANT COSTUME.
- ( sighs )
- HEY, AYEKA.
- OH, TENCHI, HAVE I REALLY
DONE SOMETHING SO HORRIFIC
TO DRIVE YOU TO THIS?
- STAY HERE.
AND DON'T GO SNEAKING
BACK OVER TO TOKYO.
- ( whimpering )
- ( girls giggling )
- SO THIS IS
THE SOUVENIR YOU WANT?
YOU KNOW, IT'S MY
FAVORITE ONE TOO.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DO THAT
WITH HER AS WELL.
NASTY YOU!
- MEOW!
- HEY!  I'VE GOT IT.
SOME POWERFUL
SUPERNATURAL AGENT
IS MANIPULATING
MY REPORT DEVICES.
- WHAT?
- FROM WHERE?
- IT'S EXACTLY HALFWAY
BETWEEN TOKYO AND HERE.
I HAVE TO GO THERE TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S DOING IT.
- GREAT.  LET'S GO.
- OH, MY.
- FIRE UP THAT PET OF OURS.
- BUT, RYOKO,
TENCHI SAID HE WANTED US
TO WAIT FOR HIM HERE.
- ( grunts )
- DON'T COME TO TOKYO.
- ARGH!  DON'T BE SUCH
A GOODY-TWO-SHOES.
AS LONG AS WE DON'T GO
TO TOKYO, WE'LL BE FINE.
- RIGHT.
OKAY, RYO-OHKI,
YOU READY?
- MEOW.
MEOW!
- LET'S GO.
- STRAIGHT AHEAD,
RYO-OHKI.
- MEOW!
- Ryoko: I DON'T KNOW
WHO YOU ARE,
BUT I DON'T TAKE
BEING MADE A FOOL OF LIGHTLY.
- THEY'LL SOON LEARN
THAT I AIN'T JOKING.
I SENSE HEARTS
WAITING TO BE BROKEN.
I WON'T BE SABOTAGED.
PREPARE TO HAVE YOUR LOVE
ANNIHILATED.
- SOMETHING'S HEADED
OUR WAY, RYOKO.
- HMM.
- ( growling )
- WE'RE STILL OUTSIDE
OF TOKYO, RYOKO,
SO IT SHOULD BE OKAY.
- LOOK AT THAT.
WHO ARE YOU?
AND WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
- MY NAME IS ZUMINO.
I AM THE GREAT SPIRIT
OF CELLULAR PHONES
AND OTHER CORDLESS DEVICES.
- THERE'S A SPIRIT
FOR EVERYTHING.
- HE DOESN'T
LOOK HAPPY.
- ( grunts )
THE BATTERED AND ANGUISHED SOULS
OF THE MANY MEN DUMPED
OVER THE CELLULAR PHONE
HAS DRIVEN ME TO THIS
DRASTIC AND FINAL MEASURE.
- MEOW!
- LONG-DISTANCE LOVE
IS FORBIDDEN,
AND YOU WILL NOT DEFY ME.
YAH!
LONG-DISTANCE LOVE
IS EVIL!
IT IS FORBIDDEN!
- MEOW!
- SASAMI, GET IN
CLOSER TO HIM.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT
HIS LASER BEAM?
- CLOSER!
GET SET, BUDDY,
'CAUSE WE'RE GONNA BLAST YOU.
OH, YOU'LL BE SORRY
THAT YOU EVER TRIED
TO MAKE A MOCKERY
OF MY LOVE FOR TENCHI.
- MEOW!
- ( grunting )
IT IS FORBIDDEN.
- WATCH OUT!
- NOW WE'VE GOT HIM.
OH!
- MEOW!
- ( screams )
- ( laughs )
THAT'LL TEACH THEM TO MESS
WITH A BIG PURPLE MONSTER.
- Ryoko: HEY, TALL STUFF.
- HUH?
- HA!
- ( grunting )
- NICE BOW YOU'VE GOT,
BIG BOY.
DID YOUR MAMA
BUY THAT FOR YOU, HUH?
- MY LASERS
DON'T WORK ON HER.
- THAT'S RIGHT.  AND NEITHER
DOES YOUR CHARM, BUD.
- ( monster babbling )
- YES!
- ( birds chirping )
- OH?
ALIENS ARE FALLING
FROM THE SKY.
- OH, I'M NOTHING BUT A FIGMENT
OF YOUR IMAGINATION.  BYE.
- ( laughing )
WELL, AT LEAST WE PUT AN END
TO THE SPYING.
- GEE, WASHU, YOU SURE KNOW
HOW TO PUT US IN DANGER.
- NOW I KNOW
WHERE WE WENT WRONG.
AND I HAVE ENOUGH DATA
TO MAKE A NEW PROTOTYPE.
- HOW'S EVERYONE
DOING IN HERE?
- IT'S YOU!
- WHOO!  HI, TENCHI.
- IT'S GOOD
TO SEE YOU.
- PRIEST DOKUZEN
GAVE ME THESE COOKIES
AND I THOUGHT WE COULD ALL
SHARE THEM TOGETHER.
AND YOU LIKE SWEETS.
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S SWEET.
- ( both scream )
- I WAS SO WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
OH, YOU HAVE NO IDEA
AT ALL, TENCHI.
WE DIDN'T KNOW
IF YOU WERE ALL RIGHT OR--
OR IF WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU
OR IF YOU WERE HURT
OR IF YOU NEEDED HELP.
( sobbing )
- HMM?
- WELL, I'LL GET
SOME MILK
TO GO WITH THE COOKIES
TENCHI BROUGHT US.
- I'LL HELP.
- DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TODAY?
WHY IS EVERYBODY
ACTING WEIRD?
- UH, MM...
NOTHING HAPPENED.
IT WAS JUST
A LONG DAY.
- FOR ME TOO.
- REALLY?
( giggles )
- ( upbeat song playing )
- MEOW, MEOW.
MEOW.
- HI.  I'M SASAMI.
WHAT?  TENCHI'S GETTING
MARRIED TO SAKUYA?
HOORAY!  I'D BE VERY HAPPY
TO HEAR WEDDING BELLS.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS
THAT IF RYOKO
AND MY SISTER AYEKA
EVER FIND OUT ABOUT THIS,
THEY WOULD
REALLY BE UPSET.
I BET THEY'D FIGHT
TO THE DEATH.
THAT'S NOT ALL
THAT'S GOING ON.
SOMETHING IS NOT
QUITE RIGHT.
WHAT KIND OF PLACE
IS THIS MANSION?
I DON'T HAVE A GOOD FEELING
ABOUT IT.
THE NEXT EPISODE OF THE NEW
"TENCHI MUYO" SERIES,
"THE ETERNAL PLEDGE."