- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( Yugi laughs )
IT'S STARTING NOW.
IT'LL HAPPEN VERY SOON.
( laughs )
- Noboyuki:
IT'S GONE!
GONE! GONE! GONE! GONE!
IT CAN'T BE!
LET'S SEE.
NO, IT'S NOT IN THIS ONE.
NOPE, NOT THIS ONE.
NO, NO, NO, NO!
IT JUST VANISHED.
- LA, LA, LA, LA.
- ( meowing )
- AH, SASAMI.
- HUH?
- I SEEM TO HAVE
LOST SOMETHING HERE.
IT'S ABOUT THIS BIG.
- ( squeaks )
- ( groans )
AH! I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT AN ENVELOPE THAT
WAS ALL FULL OF MONEY.
I NEVER SET EYES ON IT.
WELL, GOT TO GO.
- ALL RIGHT.
WELL, THANKS ANYWAY
FOR YOUR HELP.
BUT WHERE COULD
IT HAVE GONE?
- CHOCOLATE, CANDIES,
AND THE COOKIES.
- WE'RE NOT GOING
ON A PICNIC.
WE'RE GOING TO SEE TENCHI.
THIS IS SERIOUS.
NOW I WANT YOU TO LEAVE ALL
THESE SNACKS HERE, MIHOSHI.
- OKAY, BUT YOU WOULDN'T CALL
THESE BANANAS SNACKS, WOULD YOU?
- OF COURSE THEY ARE.
- OH, HOW ABOUT APPLES?
- THEY'RE SNACKS.
- NOT THESE ORANGES.
- SNACKS.
- WATERMELON? COCONUT?
( grunts )
- THEY'RE SNACKS
AND WE'RE
NOT TAKING THEM.
- Ayeka:
ATTENTION, EVERYONE.
THANKS TO FATHER'S KIND,
IF UNINTENDED, CONTRIBUTION,
WE NOW HAVE ENOUGH MONEY
TO MAKE THIS TRIP.
THE TIME HAS COME
AT LONG LAST
TO CROSS THAT THRESHOLD.
TENCHI MUST TELL US
HIS HONEST FEELINGS
AND THEN WE WILL
ALL KNOW THE TRUTH.
- NICE SPEECH IF
YOU LIKE GARBAGE.
- HMM?
YOU WOULDN'T BE
TALKING TO ME NOW,
WOULD YOU, RYOKO?
- NO.
I'M TALKING TO SOME OTHER
CLUELESS SPACE PRINCESS.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE UP TO,
BUT YOU'RE FORGETTING
THAT TENCHI
WENT TO TOKYO TO STUDY.
AS SERIOUS AS HE IS,
YOU REALLY THINK
HE'D GO AND GET INVOLVED
WITH THAT LITTLE FLIRT
SAKUYA?
NOT TENCHI.
NO WAY.
- WELL, I'M SURE
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S BEST, DEAR.
- NO DOUBT TENCHI'S
MADE SOME NEW FRIENDS.
THAT'S ONLY NATURAL.
HE HAS HIS OWN SOCIAL LIFE
AND IF YOU INTERFERE WITH IT,
I BET HE'S GOING TO BE
REALLY ANGRY WITH YOU,
CAPISCE?
- ( growls )
THAT'S ACTUALLY QUITE
UNDERSTANDING OF YOU, RYOKO.
- I AM VERY UNDERSTANDING
BECAUSE I BELIEVE IN TENCHI
UNLIKE A CERTAIN SELFISH
JURAI PRINCESS WE ALL KNOW.
- I BELIEVE IN HIM.
BUT MY BELIEFS AND FEELINGS
ARE TWO DIFFERENT THINGS.
MY FEELINGS ARE OVERWHELMING.
THAT'S WHY I NEED
TO SEE LORD TENCHI
AND FIND OUT HOW HE FEELS.
I SIMPLY HAVE GOT
TO KNOW THE TRUTH.
- FINE, DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- DON'T WORRY, I WILL.
- COME ON, EVERYONE.
WE'RE GOING TO SHIBUYA.
- ON OUR WAY.
- ( fireworks pop )
- DON'T MISS THE LIVE CONCERT
AT 2:00 PM.
AND WELCOME TO
THE SCHOOL CARNIVAL.
- ( sizzling )
- ( popping )
- Sugano:
DELICIOUS CREPES RIGHT HERE.
GET 'EM WHILE THEY'RE HOT.
- ( grunts )
- Umanosuke: YO', TENCHI.
THEY GOT YOU WORKING, HUH?
- ( gasps )
- YOU'RE HELPING SAKUYA,
AREN'T YOU?
STIRRING THE DOUGH FOR HER,
THAT'S A GOOD MOVE.
- WELL, YEAH, SHE'S GOT
THIS FOOD BOOTH, YOU KNOW?
AND SHE NEEDED SOME HELP
SO I KIND OF VOLUNTEERED.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
I BET YOU DID.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I WAS PLANNING ON DOING
MUCH THE SAME THING.
HMM, HMM, HMM, HMM.
I'VE ALSO DECIDED I'M GONNA
ASK A GIRL TO GO STEADY TONIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, TENCHI?
- HUH?
- YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
IF YOU GET ROMANTIC
WITH A GIRL
AFTER THE SCHOOL CARNIVAL,
SHE'LL FALL FOR YOU
LIKE A TON OF BRICKS.
YOU'VE HEARD ALL THE STORIES,
HAVEN'T YOU?
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- YEAH.
I GUESS I HEARD
SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
- Girl: HELLO, THERE.
- Both: HUH?
- HURRY UP WITH THAT FISH,
COME ON.
- JUST A SECOND.
WISH ME LUCK. OH, AND GOOD
LUCK TO YOU WITH SAKUYA TOO.
WE'LL BE RIGHT THERE,
ME AND THE FISH THAT IS.
- WHAT IS HE DOING
WITH THAT THING?
WELL, MAYBE I DON'T
WANT TO KNOW.
- HEY, YOU'RE NOT
EVEN STIRRING, TENCHI.
COME ON, WE'RE RUNNING
OUT OF DOUGH.
- OH, RIGHT.
NO PROBLEM.
- TENCHI'S SO CUTE
WORKING LIKE THAT.
I THINK HE'S DOING
IT FOR YOU.
- HE'S NICE, ISN'T HE?
- BETTER THAN NICE.
YOU'RE LUCKY TO HAVE A BOYFRIEND
LIKE THAT, SAKUYA.
IF HE'S GOT A TWIN BROTHER,
SEND HIM MY WAY.
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, HE'S NOT MY BOYFRIEND.
- REALLY?  YOU SURE
COULD HAVE FOOLED ME
THE WAY YOU ACT AROUND HIM.
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU ASK HIM
TO GO STEADY
AFTER THE CARNIVAL?
- HUH?
BUT I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
- WHY NOT? GIRLS CAN ASK BOYS.
IT'S A TRADITION.
- I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT.
I'M SELLING FOOD, HERE.
I'M NOT LOOKING
FOR A BOYFRIEND.
- RIGHT, THAT'S WHY YOU
WERE BLUSHING A MINUTE AGO.
- ( groans )
THE CREPE IS BURNING.
- Sugano: GIVE IT TO ME.
OOH, OUCH!
- HEY, DON'T BREAK THE DISHES.
- ( dish breaks )
- ( doorbell rings )
- LORD, TENCHI.
LORD TENCHI?
HE'S NOT ANSWERING THE DOOR.
I WONDER WHERE HE IS.
I MEAN, IT'S SUNDAY.
HE SHOULD DEFINITELY BE HOME
STUDYING OR DOING HOMEWORK
OR SOMETHING.
- HE WASN'T AT
THE TSUCHIDA SHRINE.
SO WHERE ELSE
MIGHT HE HAVE GONE?
- IT'S LUNCHTIME SO HE MUST
HAVE GONE OUT TO LUNCH.
YEAH, THAT'S NATURAL.
- WE SHOULD HAVE
TOLD HIM WE WERE COMING.
WHY DOES IT HAVE
TO BE A BIG MYSTERY.
IF YOU ASK ME, YOU GIRLS
ARE GETTING REALLY WEIRD.
- WE'RE NOT WEIRD.
IT'S JUST WITH SAKUYA AROUND,
TENCHI DOESN'T ALWAYS
TELL US WHAT'S HAPPENING.
THAT'S THE POINT.
WE HAD TO COME LIKE THIS
WITHOUT WARNING.
THIS WAY, WE'LL FIND OUT
WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON.
TENCHI WILL HAVE
TO TELL US THE TRUTH.
- SO ARE WE GONNA STAND HERE
AND MAKE SPEECHES
OR ARE WE GONNA GO INSIDE
AND WAIT FOR TENCHI?
- BUT WE DON'T
HAVE THE KEY.
- KEY'S ARE SO OLD-FASHIONED.
THIS IS MUCH BETTER.
CHECK IT OUT,
MY NEW POWER GLOVE.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasping )
- SEE, IT'S EASY.
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
YOU KNOW YOU WANT TO SEE IT.
COME ON IN.
- IT'S EMPTY.
TENCHI REALLY ISN'T HERE.
NOT THAT I THOUGHT HE
WAS AVOIDING US OR ANYTHING
BY PRETENDING
NOT TO BE HERE.
- WELL, SINCE WE DON'T KNOW
WHERE HE WENT,
I GUESS WE'LL JUST
HAVE TO SIT DOWN
AND WAIT UNTIL
HE COMES BACK HOME.
- ( meows )
- YES, WE DON'T HAVE ANY CHOICE.
- ( meowing )
- WHOA, WHAT IS IT, RYO-OHKI?
- Ayeka: OOH, IT'S A FLYER
FOR A SCHOOL CARNIVAL.
- ( chattering )
- Tenchi: WOW,
IT LOOKS DELICIOUS.
- GO AHEAD.
DIG IN, TENCHI.
- DON'T MIND IF I DO.
- IS IT ALL RIGHT?
- HMM, IT'S GOOD.
I'VE NEVER TASTED
ANYTHING SO DELICIOUS.
- OKAY.
I'M TAKING CULINARY LESSONS,
YOU KNOW?
IT'S GOURMET CUISINE.
- I GET THE PICTURE.
HUH?
- OH.
( laughs )
- ( both laugh )
- OH, TENCHI, YOU WANT TO GO SEE
THAT CONCERT TOGETHER?
- CONCERT?
- YEAH, AT 2:00 IN THE GYM,
IT'S A LIVE BAND.
COME ON, IT'LL BE FUN.
- WELL, I'D LIKE TO GO,
BUT WHAT ABOUT
YOUR FOOD BOOTH?
YOU KNOW, THE CREPES
AND EVERYTHING?
- OH, I DON'T THINK
WE'LL HAVE ANY CUSTOMERS THEN.
I MEAN, EVERYONE WILL BE
AT THE CONCERT.
REMEMBER,
THIS IS OUR CARNIVAL.
YOU GOT TO BE TRUE TO YOUR
SCHOOL AND ALL THAT, RIGHT?
- WELL, WHEN YOU
PUT IT LIKE THAT,
HOW CAN I REFUSE?
LET'S DO IT.
- HM-HMM.
- ( laughing )
- ( meowing )
- ( crowd chatters )
- COME ON, KIYONE,
BUY ME SOME FOOD.
OH, PLEASE, I'M SO HUNGRY.
THEY'VE GOT CREPES HERE,
AND FRIED NOODLES...
AND THE SHISH KABOB
LOOKS GOOD TOO.
- FORGET IT, MIHOSHI.
I'M NOT PAYING
FOR YOUR SNACKS.
- ( cries )
- WE'VE LOOKED ALL OVER,
BUT I DON'T SEE
LORD TENCHI ANYWHERE.
I WONDER WHERE HE IS.
- WITH ALL THESE
PEOPLE HERE,
IT'S LIKE LOOKING FOR
A NEEDLE IN A HAYSTACK.
- BUT HE HAS TO
BE HERE SOMEWHERE.
THIS IS HIS SCHOOL.
HE WOULDN'T MISS
THEIR BIG CARNIVAL.
WHY DON'T WE SPLIT UP?
WE'LL HAVE A BETTER CHANCE
OF FINDING HIM.
- ( smirks )
LOOKS LIKE FUN, DOESN'T IT?
- ( birds twitter )
- MIYUKI, DEAR.
- DOCTOR.
- Narrator: AT LAST,
MIYUKI HAD FOUND TRUE LOVE.
NOW HER ONLY WISH
WAS THAT HIS HAPPINESS
COULD LAST FOREVER AND EVER.
HOW COULD SHE HAVE KNOWN
THAT IN THE NEXT INSTANT,
A SUPER, GIANT METEOR
WOULD CRASH INTO JAPAN.
- ( explosion )
- RIGHT, IT'S
ALWAYS A METEOR.
( slurps )
AND NOTHING LEFT TO EAT
BUT INSTANT NOODLES.
( swallows )
WITH SASAMI GONE, THERE'S NO
ONE HERE TO COOK DINNER.
I'M CERTAINLY NOT
GOING TO DO IT.
IT'S BENEATH
A SPACE PIRATE'S DIGNITY.
MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE
GONE WITH THEM
EVEN IF THEY ARE ANNOYING.
- OH, RYOKO, THERE YOU ARE.
- I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT
A MISSING ENVELOPE
FULL OF MONEY.
SO DON'T DARE ASK.
- OH, I SEE.
WELL, I WONDER WHERE
IT COULD HAVE GONE.
- ( sighs )
I WISH I KNEW WHAT TENCHI
WAS DOING RIGHT NOW.
- ( crowd chatters )
- I BETTER HURRY.
I PROMISED SAKUYA
I'D MEET HER
FOR THE CONCERT.
AHH!
IT CAN'T BE.
AYEKA?
NO, I'M JUST
IMAGINING THINGS.
THE DIMENSION TUNNEL'S SEALED.
THEY CAN'T COME HERE.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
FUNNY HOW YOUR MIND
CAN TRICK YOU.
( laughs )
- Sasami: RYO-OHKI!
- ( groans )
- RYO-OHKI!
RYO-OHKI, WAIT FOR ME!
- THERE HERE.
- ( meows )
- THIS IS BAD.
WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE THEY UP TO?
- ( frightened mutters )
- OH NO! THAT'S A GUN.
- ( whimpers )
- OH, SHE SHOT MY BOOTH.
- OH MY GOD.
- ( whispering )
- WOW, HOW COULD I MISS
AN EASY TARGET LIKE THAT?
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
WRONG WITH MY BLASTER.
- THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
WITH YOUR HEAD, MIHOSHI.
- Tenchi: WHAT ARE
YOU TWO DOING HERE?
- HUH?
- OH, HI, TENCHI.
- WE'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
I GUESS YOU HEARD
THE GUNSHOT.
- THIS BETTER BE GOOD,
MIHOSHI.
NOW WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( excited exclaims )
- ( meowing )
- THE SCIENCE LAB!
- EUREKA! A NEW DISCOVERY!
WHO COULD HAVE IMAGINED
RIGHT HERE AT OUR SCHOOL,
I'VE DISCOVERED
A NEW SPECIES OF RODENT?
I'M GONNA BE
RICH AND FAMOUS.
THEY'LL NEVER
MAKE FUN OF ME AGAIN.
THEY CALLED ME NERDO,
FOUR-EYES, MOUTH-BREATHER.
BUT NOW I'LL GO DOWN
IN HISTORY AS RODENT-MAN.
- ( meowing )
- SOMEBODY CATCH THAT THING.
I'M GOING TO BE ON
DAYTIME TALK SHOWS.
THE PAPARAZZI WILL
BE ALL OVER ME.
STOP! TALK TO MY AGENT FIRST.
- ( meowing )
- NO ESCAPE! HIYAH!
- ( meows )
- NOW, MY LITTLE
RODENT SPECIMEN,
WE WILL NEVER FORGET
THE VALIANT SACRIFICE
YOU ARE ABOUT TO MAKE FOR
THE ADVANCEMENT OF SCIENCE,
THE ADVANCEMENT OF MANKIND,
AND THE ADVANCEMENT
OF MY OWN CAREER.
- ( meowing )
( meowing )
- ( screams )
- WHAT'S GOING ON IN THERE?
- WHO CARES?
IT'S TIME FOR THE CONCERT.
- ( grunts )
- ( yelps )
- OH, TENCHI, IT'S YOU.
- RYO-OHKI IS IN SOME
KIND OF TROUBLE.
- I KNOW.
- ( explosions )
- ( panting )
( shouts )
- RYO-OHKI.
- ( meows )
- CALM DOWN.
EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE SAFE NOW, RYO-OHKI.
- DON'T MOVE. WE'LL GET
SOME MEDICS UP HERE.
JUST HANG IN THERE.
- ( whimpers )
TELL THE PAPARAZZI
( shudders )
I DID IT FOR SCIENCE.
- EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
NO ONE'S GONNA HURT YOU NOW.
- RYO-OHKI, LOOK AT
THE DAMAGE YOU'VE DONE.
- ( meows )
- ( explosion )
- ( screams )
OH NO.  WHAT NEXT?
- SO DOES IT WORK?
- UM, NO,
IT'S TOTALLY BROKEN.
HUH?
- OH, WELL, WELL,
THIS IS SUCH AN
OLD-FASHIONED SENSOR
AND THE MOTOR'S JUST A TOY.
IN ANY ENLIGHTENED PLANET
LIKE JURAI,
YOU COULDN'T GIVE AWAY
A RAT GADGET LIKE THIS.
NOW, LET'S SEE.
- ( thinking )
WHAT HAPPENED TO TENCHI?
HE WAS SUPPOSED
TO MEET ME HERE.
- Tenchi: DON'T YOU THINK
YOU'VE GONE A LITTLE TOO FAR?
- Ayeka: IT'S NOT MY
FAULT, TENCHI. REALLY.
THESE PEOPLE LIED TO ME.
THEY TOLD ME YOU WERE INSIDE.
AND THEN THEY SCARED ME
WITH THOSE TRICKS.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO WRECK EVERYTHING.
I JUST WANTED TO FIND YOU.
- AYEKA!
- ( gasps )
- THEY WORKED SO HARD
TO BUILD THIS FOR THE CARNIVAL
AND YOU HAD TO DESTROY IT.
THEY WEREN'T TRYING
TO SCARE YOU.
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE FUN.
- I'M SORRY, TENCHI.
IT'S JUST THAT
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- I WANT YOU TO GO HOME!
- OH.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT POSSESSED YOU
TO SUDDENLY INVADE MY LIFE,
BUT WE'LL JUST HAVE TO TALK
ABOUT IT LATER.
WAIT FOR ME AT MY APARTMENT
AND TRY NOT TO WRECK ANYTHING
IN THE MEAN TIME.
- ( motor whirrs )
- ( groans )
DON'T--
DON'T TELL ME YOU BROUGHT
WASHU HERE WITH YOU.
- HM-HMM.
- HEAVEN HELP US.
- Girl: LOOK OUT!
SHE TURNED THAT SENSOR
INTO A GIANT RAT.
- WELL, EVERYONE'S
GONE OFF TO THE CONCERT
SO I CAN FINALLY RELAX
A LITTLE BIT.
THANK GOODNESS FOR THAT.
- ( motor whirrs )
- HUH?
WHAT'S THAT NOISE?
HMM?  A GIANT RAT
IS COMING THIS WAY.
- ( crashing )
- WHOA!
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
( groans )
- Girls:
( sigh )
- SO IT BUMPS INTO THINGS.
I THOUGHT I FIXED IT
BEFORE I ENLARGED IT,
BUT, WELL, YOU CAN
ONLY DO SO MUCH
WITH THIS
INFERIOR TECHNOLOGY.
- WASHU!
- HI, TENCHI.
HOW'S IT GOING?
- IT'S GOING BAD. WHAT IS THAT?
- IT'S JUST A LITTLE GADGET
THE SCIENCE STUDENTS HAD.
I KIND OF BEEFED IT UP
A LITTLE BIT.
I THOUGHT THE STUDENTS
WOULD GET A THRILL
AND, YOU KNOW,
TEACH THEM SOMETHING
ABOUT ADVANCED SCIENCE.
BUT IT DIDN'T QUITE MAKE IT
THROUGH THE MAZE.
- THE SCHOOL'S NOT A MAZE.
YOU'VE GOT TO STOP IT.
- WELL, THAT'S KIND
OF A PROBLEM.
YOU SEE, I REMOVED
THE ON AND OFF SWITCH
'CAUSE IT WAS IN MY WAY
AND IT LOOKED FUNNY.
SO NOW WE'LL JUST HAVE TO LET
THE BATTERIES RUN OUT, YOU KNOW?
- ALL I KNOW IS THAT
YOU ARE A MENACE, WASHU.
- ( rat tires screech )
- ( gasps )
- TENCHI WOULDN'T
STAND ME UP.
AT LEAST I DON'T
THINK HE WOULD.
- ( panting )
- MAYBE HE JUST DOESN'T
CARE ABOUT ME.
MAYBE I'VE BEEN ALL WRONG.
I GUESS I'LL JUST LEAVE.
- ( shrieks )
- ( crashing )
- ( gasps )
- RUN, SAKUYA, RUN!
AH!
- ( explosion )
- WHOA.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- WHEW, THAT WAS CLOSE,
BUT WE STOPPED HIM.
RIGHT, TENCHI?
HUH?
HMM?
OH MY.
- TENCHI!
- YOU'RE NOT HURT OR ANYTHING,
ARE YOU, TENCHI?
- I CAN'T TAKE ANYMORE!
STOP IT!
- ( gasps )
- BUT WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
TENCHI?
- JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
- ( gasps )
- I WANT YOU ALL
TO GO BACK HOME.
- BUT WE CAME TO SEE YOU.
- YOU'RE NOTHING BUT TROUBLE,
ALL OF YOU.
- BUT YOU MEAN--
- YOU HEARD WHAT HE SAID.
( whimpers )
WELL, COME ON, EVERYONE.
LET'S GO.
- Girls:
( sighs )
- TENCHI, THEY'RE LEAVING.
- HMM.
I HAD TO COME AND SAVE
TENCHI FROM THOSE GIRLS.
THEY'RE PROBABLY DRIVING HIM
CRAZY BY NOW.
SO HERE IT GOES.
OH, WHAT'S THIS?
HEY, TENCHI.
ARE YOU HERE?
( gasps )
NOBODY'S HOME.
I GUESS.
- ( fire crackling )
- I SEE, THEY CAME
ALL THE WAY FROM OKAYAMA.
THAT'S A LONG WAY.
- HMPH, A LONG WAY
TO RUIN OUR SCHOOL CARNIVAL.
WHAT A MESS.
- OH, WELL.
IT WAS FUN FOR ME ANYWAY
WHEN WE WORKED TOGETHER
AT THE FOOD BOOTH.
THAT WAS THE BEST PART
OF THE WHOLE DAY.
- BUT YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
THE BOOTH--
- DESTROYED, I KNOW.
BUT THEY WOULD HAVE
TORN IT DOWN ANYWAY.
AT LEAST WE HAD A GOOD TIME
WHILE IT WAS THERE.
- I GUESS.
- TENCHI,
THIS WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
THERE'S NO REASON
FOR YOU TO FEEL BAD.
( gasps )
OH WOW.
- WHAT IS IT?
- OH, I DIDN'T EVEN
TAKE THE TIME TO THANK THEM
FOR SAVING ME
FROM THAT RAT THING.
I JUST TOTALLY FORGOT.
- UGH!
YOU DON'T NEED
TO THANK THEM.
THEY CAUSED THE WHOLE THING.
- THEY DIDN'T MEAN TO.
AND THEY TRIED
TO MAKE UP FOR IT.
I'LL THANK THEM THE NEXT TIME
THAT I SEE THEM.
OKAY?
- ( sighs )
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
- HM-HMM.
- SAKUYA, ARE YOU COLD?
- ( sighs )
NOT REALLY.
I THINK I FEEL
KIND OF LONELY
'CAUSE THE CARNIVAL'S OVER.
- I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
- TENCHI.
- YES, SAKUYA?
- THEY SAY THAT
AFTER THE CARNIVAL,
YOU SHOULD GO TO
THE ONE YOU LOVE
AND TELL HIM HOW
YOU FEEL ABOUT HIM.
I WASN'T GONNA DO THAT
'CAUSE, WELL, I DON'T BELIEVE
IN THOSE SCHOOL LEGENDS.
IF I CAN BE WITH YOU
EVERY DAY
LIKE WE ARE AT SCHOOL,
THAT'S ENOUGH
TO MAKE ME HAPPY.
AND I MEAN THAT.
I REALLY DO.
BUT THEN, SOMETIMES
WHEN I'M FEELING CLOSE TO YOU,
SUDDENLY I'LL
FEEL SO FAR AWAY.
THAT'S HOW I FELT TODAY
WHEN YOU GOT ANGRY
AT THOSE GIRLS.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
YOU SO SERIOUS.
AND I COULD TELL THAT,
SOMEHOW,
THIS WAS REALLY
IMPORTANT TO YOU
IN A SPECIAL WAY.
WHEN I REALIZED THAT,
I SUDDENLY FELT
SO JEALOUS OF THEM.
YES, I WAS JEALOUS
AND ALSO...
IT MADE ME SAD.
- OH.
SAKUYA.
- WHAT AM I DOING?
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO SAY ALL THAT.
THERE'S SO MUCH
GOING ON NOW.
I GUESS I'M JUST A LITTLE
CONFUSED RIGHT NOW.
SORRY.
- ( fire crackling )
- KISSY KISSY, LOVEY-DOVEY.
EVERYWHERE YOU LOOK,
IT'S THE SAME THING.
WHAT'S UP
WITH THIS SCHOOL?
AND WHERE'S TENCHI ANYWAY?
IT'S LIKE HE VANISHED.
MAYBE HE WENT
BACK HOME ALREADY.
( sighs )
TENCHI, TENCHI.
( gasps )
AH, HMM.
HMM.
( whimpers )
( growls )
HOW DARE YOU DO THIS.
- ( gasps )
- OH.
OH.
- AT LAST, THE BONDS
THAT HOLD THEM TOGETHER
ARE COMING APART.
IT'S THE BEGINNING OF THE END
FOR HIS WHOLE FAMILY.
( chuckles )
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( meowing )
( meows )
- Washu: HELLO,
YOUR DARLING WASHU HERE.
HMM, I SEE WHY THIS HOUSE
SEEMS SO QUIET.
RYOKO'S GONE.
WELL, I WOULDN'T WORRY
ABOUT HER AT ALL.
I KNOW HER. SHE'LL BE BACK
WHEN SHE FEELS LIKE IT.
IN THE MEAN TIME,
I'LL KEEP MYSELF
BUSY IN MY LAB
DOING SOME
IMPORTANT RESEARCH.
DON'T DISTURB ME, OKAY?
THE NEXT EPISODE OF
THE NEW TENCHI MUYO SERIES...
"DRIFTING AWAY."