Oh lovely rose about to bloom,
on a pale, moonlit night...
Your petals dripping red
Your leaves lithe and green.
Your lustrous
fragrance fills the air
Receive my blood...
Let it flow through your lips
Drink it, taste
it with your tongue
Quench your thirst...
before you wither... and die.
No... do not wither and die.
Master Toma...
What are your intentions?
What will you do now?
That which I loved
most was taken from me...
And I must take that
same love in return.
He is ready...
I have but to show him the path.
That red path has
to mean something.
I don't know what it means...
but it sure smelled sweet.
Apollo?
You're talkin' about that bright
red path to the moon, right?
Almost made me sick
how sweet it smelled...
But, there was somethin'
familiar about it, too...
Commander...?
Is there something on your mind?
The time has come when
all must choose their path...
Guess you couldn't sleep either?
No... I was in the middle of
having a dream when I woke up...
Really... Me too...
A nightmare...
Thousands of dancing feathers...
I understand...
I think the child Shadow Angel's
death is weighing heavily
on everyone's
conscience right now.
No, no... it was more than that.
I saw Glen! He was in pain!
The feathers were
attacking him...!
His body was gray
and withered...!
Reika... There's something
I need to ask you...
Sure, anything, Sirius...
What would you do if you
learned of a shadow angel...
...right here, among us?
Fight with all my strength...
...no matter what...!
Shadow angels are the enemy!
Why? What's wrong?
Nothing... I was being
rhetorical... Good night.
Who is it?
I'm sorry to bother you.
It's just me...
May I come in?
It's late Silvia...
What do you need?
It's silly... I was
having a bad dream...
I see... You're
not the only one.
Tell me... What did you see?
I'm not sure...
It was twelve thousand years ago
when humanity first stood
against the Shadow Angels ...
I was watching
Solar Wing from a distance...
He was heading out
for the final battle.
The Battle of Atlandia...
As he flew away into the sky,
red feathers fell from his body
and rained down
upon the earth...
He disappeared
with a flash of light
and never returned again...
As I watched Solar Wing
it felt as though
you were the one leaving.
Don't worry... You and I will
always be together Silvia.
I know that...
Why wouldn't we...
We spent so much time here...
Remember how
reclusive we used to be?
But things are
different now, aren't they?
You've managed to make
friends with the others...
You're not such an
outsider anymore...
Believe it or not,
neither are you, brother,
even though I still can't
get you to eat with us...
Everyone thinks
of you as a friend.
They all trust you and
respect your intelligence.
Sometimes I wonder.
Well there's nothing
to wonder about...
It took time, but we're
a part of the group now.
Both of us.
Listen... why don't you join us
for just one meal tomorrow...?
Your pick.
You know my feelings
on eating in public...
It lacks elegance.
Oh right. I forgot.
This armor is so beautiful...
I bet it would look
amazing on you.
It's an imitation.
Along with everything
in this room...
Including myself...
When I think about
my place in DEAVA I just...
Sometimes I just
wonder if there is one.
It's late... I'll walk you back.
Brother...
Do you think we
could talk again soon?
Of course.
You're eating again?!
You got a problem?
Yeah!
Walking around
with your mouth stuffed
full of food like
that--it's uncivilized...!
Isn't that right, brother?
I'm curious, Apollo, why is
it you're always so hungry?
Are you that unfulfilled?
Huh?
You appear to be masking
your lack of fulfillment
by constantly gorging yourself.
What the hell...?
I eat when I get
hungry--that's it...
There's no reason to it...
A human's actions should
be guided by reason...
It separates us from animals
Yeah, my life's eating,
sleeping and fighting.
I don't have time for
this psycho-babble crap.
You're wasting
your time, brother.
The only reason Apollo has
for doing anything
is the way it smells.
He lets his nose do all
of his thinking for him.
What's wrong with that?
I got a good nose, so I use it.
Apollo... Tell me something.
Yeah? What?
What does your keen nose
sense when you smell me?
Forget it...
I don't want to know.
I'm sorry I bothered you.
Okay?
Brother, wait up.
Where are you going...
And you!
Don't come crying to me when you
get a bellyache from overeating!
"Overeating?!" I don't
even know that word!
Who are you?
I just spoke with Apollo...
Apparently, he saw
something last night...
Some sort of red path,
stretching up into the sky...
The crimson path.
This looks fun.
I'll bet it's one of our new
special training exercises.
The Crimson Path...
It existed in ancient times...
as a link from earth...
...up into the heavens...
Solar Wing made
the path his own.
Meaning what...? Exactly?
The Crimson path is beckoning...
reaching out for Solar Wing.
What are you saying here?
It's the path that Solar
Wing will have to travel...
Yeah, that part of it I got...
Well, the story goes,
in ancient times...
I'm fine.
What is this...?
What am I feeling?
Am I envious of Apollo?
Which one of you will win
control of the red path...?
Will it be Apollo?! Or Sirius?!
The loser will be the first
of you who slips. Begin!
Stay focused...
I cannot lose this match!
Wow, sunshine... What's up?
You seem even
more tense than usual.
Get back...! It's my path!
Apollo!
Apollo...
Sirius. No.
What's he doing...?
An attack?
Shadow Angels...
High-level quantum
signature approaching...
signature approaching.
Elements stand by...
Vector docking
sequence complete!
Status check:
all systems green...
Power levels confirmed...
Vectors, ready for launch...
Prepare for launch
track activation...
Clear for take-off...
Initiating countdown sequence...
In 5... 4... 3...
2... 1... Launch!
Vector Mars. Taking off!
Vector Luna. Taking off!
Let's go!
Launch complete...
Vectors airborne.
Initiating barrier fields.
Quantum signature levels at 300.
No wait... They're at 320,000!
320, 000...?! It's got
to be a false reading!
No sir...
And the enemy's power
is still increasing.
It can't be.
I'm worried...
What if this Cheribum is piloted
by another
Shadow Angel Child...?
Silvia, Stay focused.
If you're having doubts,
better switch out now.
I'm not switching out!
What the?
What on earth... was that?
Stay calm!
Mount defense weaponry
and engage the enemy!
Fire!
What the hell is that?
Some new kind of Cherubim?!
Could it be an
actual shadow angel?
It doesn't matter!
We can't withstand that
kind of firepower for long!
Elements, stop that
thing at all costs!
Yeah, like you need
to tell us that.
We have to merge, now!
Okay. I'm the head!
Not this time... Silvia.
Roger. Merge one!
This is lame... Merge Two!
Go Aquarion!
I feel an ominous presence.
Brother!
Aquarion Mars!
It's so beautiful.
Sirius, what are you doing?
So we gonna fight or what?
Right, yes... Let's do this!
Amazing... like
nothing I've ever seen!
This presence... could it be...?
My best stroke, and he
parried it like it was nothing.
It's him... the angel...
That sound... Oh no...
Solar Wing...
It's been far too long.
Hey...! What the
hell are you doing?!
What's wrong, with you?
Sirius. What's gotten into you?
Let's finish him off!
Hold on...!
This isn't like him,
there's something wrong.
Screw it...! I'm done waitin'!
If he won't fight,
I will...! Dammit!
These Shadow Angels are
the ones who took Baron!
That's right Apollo, and we
took one of their children.
Something's gone wrong...
There's no unity
in their fighting.
A dark messenger
bearing seven colors
is present in this battle...
It is he who now
beckons to Solar Wing.
Messenger...
So you're saying...?!
The enemy has not come to fight.
Is Toma actually planning to
invite Solar Wing to join us?
So then... does that
mean the Shadow Angels
are gonna try to take Apollo...?
This presence...
I felt it in my dream...!
Could it be happening again...?
Noooooo!
Silvia's astral levels
are dropping rapidly!
Abnormal brain function!
She can no longer fight!
Exchange elements now...!
Reika for Silvia...! Engage!
I'm ready...!
Let's stop this thing!
Reika, we're counting on you.
The path is before you.
The first to slip
will be the loser.
Now go! Aquarion!
I knew it... It is you!
Don't deny your destiny...
Join me...
What are you waiting for?!
Fight, dammit!
Think of what
they've done to us!
All the lives they've taken!
We are equally guilty of
committing murderous acts...
The numbers bear no relevance.
What the...?
You aren't making any sense...!
The Shadow Angels
are our enemies...!
What have we been fighting for?1
The reason I fight, is to create
a world free of fighting...
where beauty prevails.
I don't understand.
What's happened to you, brother?
You've got to
snap out of it Sirius.
He's coming!
It was you, wasn't it...?
The one who beckoned to me...
What do you mean?
Sirus, listen!
Tell meeeeeee...!
The Crimson Path.
There it is again--
that same freaky scent
I picked up on last night...
This is bad...
Come on, we've gotta re-merge!
Hey! Sirius!
Don't worry. I can get him.
What are you doing, Sirius?!
Tell me! I can help you!
You'd do that?
Sirius.
Reika.
No, it can't be...
Reika... I had hoped that you,
at least, would understand...
Sirius wait.
I have made my choice!
Please don't do this...!
No! Brother, how could you?!
Forgive me... Silvia,
but my destiny was always
different from the others.
What are you talking about!
You're wrong! Turn back!
At the end of this path...
an ideal world is waiting.
It's found me at last.
Sirius!
Sirius!!
Brother!
What have you done...!
Solar Wing once
made a prediction...
These were his words:
"The path to redemption
shall be drawn in blood."
So then...
You mean my brother was
actually Solar Wing all along?
So they were your hands
I saw reaching for me...
Pulling me, to this place...
Welcome home...
Here in Atlandia your
wings will finally bloom.
The night beasts are howling...
...howling at the blue moon.
Ripping claws...
They bare sadness.
My sadness is bare.
Brother?
Next on Aquarion:
"Wings Unseen."