I'd give anything to
have a waist like yours.
It's tiny.
Oh, it's not that small.
In fact, lately I've been
gaining some weight.
I'm up two pounds
since yesterday.
What? You mean you
actually weigh yourself?
I'm too scared. I'd just die!
Tsugumi, weight control
is an important part
of our training.
We have to stay aware of
every aspect of our bodies.
If we gain too much weight,
it will affect our
ability to Merge.
It could even cost us our lives!
We could die?
Ah, finally; I'm starving.
What's wrong?
That can't really be all that
you guys are gonna eat.
We- we're trying to eat light
because Reika said we
could die if we gain weight.
We could die?!
Well no...
I just meant that
we might want to be
kind of careful about our
weight because of Aquarion...
We don't want to
risk throwing off
the equilibrium of the Merge.
Well alright, but isn't dieting
too much supposed
to be bad for you?
Look at that.
You know you wanna eat some...
Come on now,
what are you gonna do?
Just sit there and
starve yourselves?
Oh wow.
This is really good!
Now what's this...?
A princess putting on weight...
It seems she has
almost no self-control ...
What do you suppose her brother
will think about such
over-indulgence?
Disgusting.
No, wait!
Come back, Brother.
Don't leave me!
Thank you.
You feeling okay?
Normally you inhale your food.
The diet begins today.
I happen to think women are
cuter with some meat on them,
I don't know about you two.
They won't listen.
They've got their own
ideas about beauty.
Even so, they're going
about this all wrong.
Exercising constantly
and starving themselves
isn't going to help at all...
All they're going to do
is put unnecessary
stress on their bodies.
This isn't going to make
it easier for them to Merge.
If anything, it will just
make it more difficult.
Tortes, cupcakes, cookies.
It all looks so good,
and I'm so hungry.
One bite couldn't hurt.
Hold it!
We can't just give in now!
Reika...
We've done so well today,
don't we deserve a reward...?
Come on... we'll just
take one bite each,
and not tell anybody.
No... we're not undoing
all our hard work.
Drop it!
It's so good!
The wingless ones
are just revolting...
Look at them, they use
their sacred mouths
for eating while awake,
and can't even contain
themselves in their dreams.
That is the curse
of the wingless ones,
Child Angel Futaba...
From the time
they are born until
the end of their
wretched little lives,
they must gorge themselves...
They must take the lives
of all other creatures
in order to
sustain themselves...
And they are never
full, never sated.
How stupid are they
that they don't know
that the mouth is sacred
and meant only for breathing
and singing the
songs of the stars?
Disgusting.
No, brother.
I don't want to eat anymore!
No, make it go away!
Make the food go away!
Very well, wingless
gluttons. I will!
What the-
Got it!
My food!
Nooooooo!
Local teams reported that
all food has disappeared.
Reserves are depleted.
Teams are reporting
from the city sector...
All the food's gone...
It has disappeared from every
household and grocery store...
All of the crops have
withered and all the livestock
has been wiped out,
down to the last cow...
There is absolutely
no food to be found
within a fifty-mile radius.
I have a report from the
scientific investigative unit...
It seems microscopic
holes were opened
in all of the food packaging,
allowing bacteria-like
microorganisms to enter
and break down the food.
There was no way to
detect their presence.
What...?!
Are you suggesting there are
microscopic harvest beasts?
Is it true?
It's all my fault
that this happened...
I was just so worried
about how much I weighed,
and in my dream I asked
for all the food to disappear.
What now?
No one panic...
Have a reconnaissance unit
start searching for plants
and small animals in
the vicinity of the base.
Don't bother.
Just before dawn,
all the animals disappeared
from the area around
the base, even rats...
You can look for plants,
but all the edible ones
have withered and died.
The beasts have
left us with nothing.
We're receiving a
message from Command...
The provisions supply
unit is being attacked
by a harvest beast!
Mayday! Mayday!
Oh no!
Our last chance.
All the food is gone.
I'm so hungry I think I'm
starting to see things...
This morning my little stuffed
piglet looked like a pork chop.
We have to stay strong or
the Shadow Angels win...
We can just think of it
as a part of our diet.
Tsugumi, how much
weight have you lost so far?
Nothing...
I've been so hungry
and I feel so empty...
So I've been drinking water.
What...?
You mean all that is just water?
I just can't take this anymore!
My stomach keeps getting bigger
but my chest is shrinking!
If I'd known we'd gain
weight by not eating,
I wouldn't have started
that diet in the first place!
I know.
Hungry!
When I woke up this
morning I realized
that I was chewing on my pillow.
So hungry I nearly
ate it anyway.
Quit whining.
You think that we
have it bad here,
but there are many
people doing worse...
The young and healthy will
survive this the longest.
I know.
Idiot!
What the hell are you doing?
What...
A guy still gotta
eat doesn't he.
Not feet!
Prepare to attack!
Attack who?
Please excuse my boldness,
Commander,
but the harvest beasts
destroying our food
are microscopic...
How are we supposed to find,
let alone attack them?
I'm afraid you'll have to answer
that question on your own.
On our own?
Who are you gonna send?
Let us go, Commander!
Can you handle this?
We can do it...
Let us go.
Yes, please...
We want to fight!
Please sir, just let us
get our food back!
Area B 17...
I can detect no heat signatures.
Searching Area C Thirteen...
I'm getting nothing here.
Damn it, this is
just pointless...
The stupid things are too
small to detect with infrared...
Let's just Merge so
we can find them, now!
We're going to Merge?
That's right!
We don't have a choice...
If you two are ready
to begin the Merge...
Let's win our food back!
Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go... Aquarion!
Oh, wow!
I'm so hungry!
Aquarion... Luna!
Now let's go! Aquarion!
How did this happen?
Luna Element's thought
and motor functions
appear to be disconnecting.
That's only natural...
Blood sugar levels down...
Metabolism's down to the point
where thought almost stops.
Silvia!
I'm sorry... so hungry
I can barely move.
Silvia, I know...
I'm fading too.
Stop them...!
Their bodies can't
take much more of this.
They feel hunger because
they think they need to eat.
Commander...
Forgive me but is it really
time for a philosophy lesson?
Emptiness and hunger
are not the same thing.
It is through emptiness
that we find strength.
You must harness
that emptiness and fight!
Huh?
We can't.
I'm just so hungry!
What does he mean,
"harness the emptiness"...?
How do you harness
what isn't there...?
I've got it... That's
how we catch them.
That's it...
When you fast,
the emptiness causes
the rest of your senses
to become sharper.
We can use hunger
to our advantage.
What does he mean
sharpened senses?
He means scent...!
That's it... Tell them!
Silvia... Tsugumi... Reika!
Listen to me.
You have to smell them.
You have to track
them down by their scent!
Smell them?
Their scent?
They're too small for any of
our instruments to pick up...
But they didn't just destroy
our food, they ate it...!
They must have left
a trail behind them...
Sniff them out!
All right, Brother.
We'll start sniffing.
Sniffing?
If your gonna pick up
a scent, you need me.
Hey?
Incoming!
What do you think you're doing?
Doing what I do best.
Ah-ha.
Let's get 'em.
Elements ready for attack!
Go now!
Can we eat now?
What the?
It worked! We got them!
Now, Solar Wing,
I will have the great pleasure
of watching you
being eaten alive...
And I promise, I will
enjoy every minute of it.
So Aquarion, is...
...being devoured.
Stop it...!
Please stop...!
I don't taste good.
And so it goes...
We eat to survive...
until we are eaten.
What's happening...?
Are we being eaten alive?
They'll feed on us...
...until we disappear...
...and return... to the earth.
We're all done for.
I can't believe it.
Silence!
I can hear it...
The song of awakening;
the song of new life.
The earth is being replenished.
Listen to its song!
I know that voice...! Rena?
What's that?
Maybe... as Aquarion was eaten,
it's body fed the earth
and brought it to life ...
Now everything is growing again.
What's that song?
It's Rena.
I think ...
I think we Merged...
with the earth.
What's going on?
We won...!
Where are my harvest beasts?
The Tree of Life...
I didn't think this
pathetic reincarnation
of Solar Wing had the power...
Solar Wing...
I'll make him regret this.
Wow!
It's amazing.
It smells wonderful!
Delicious.
How do any of us ever
know who we really are...?
How can we find ourselves
when other people are
always getting in the way...?
I guess we're going
to find out...!
Next on Aquarion:
"Cosplay of the Soul."
You'll never recognize us!
Quiet, Sister.