As of today kid,
your name is Apollo...
Just like the
mythological god of the sun!
Apollo... Apollo!
Apollo!
Baron!
Baron...
Wait for me...
Okay, which one of you drank
my strawberry protein shake?!
Fess up!
My amulet's moving.
That's a bad omen.
Who did it?!
Probably the same person
who put teeth marks in
my Roman coin collection.
My guess? It was Apollo.
Apollo's missing!
I knew it!
Where could he have run off to?
That doesn't make him a thief...
Don't worry!
He won't stay gone long...
You're going to find him!
What?!
Man, this is getting old.
Just seem to
be going in circles.
One of these tunnels has
got to lead to the Vectors...
Attention, cadets!
Your goal is set!
The first one to find Apollo
earns the right
to pilot a Vector!
Good luck then, and go!
Oh, I forgot to mention
there are traps, so be careful.
Yeah, now she tells us...
Thanks, lady...
Well, hang in there.
Only a mongrel like
you would mistake
that Roman solidus
for a chocolate coin.
A mistake you'll soon regret.
They're actually
coming after me?!
What's this?
Decoy sounds to
throw us off track!
I'm warning you...
Don't follow me.
But my ears and my gut tell
me he's down this tunnel.
Look, if you come with me...
...you're asking...
...for bad luck.
Even if that's true...
Wouldn't your luck be
diluted with two people?
Well, am I right?
What are you doing?
Psychography.
Psych-what?
Psychic photography.
Now please be quiet.
I'm trying to concentrate here.
It's no use.
It's impossible to get a
reading because he's moving.
What are you doing?
When humans move,
they disrupt the magnetic
field and leave a trail.
I'll find Apollo in no time
all through the
power of science.
What happened?
Oh, that...? Well, um,
you see, I have this allergy...
Um... since when can an
allergy blast a hole in a wall?
It's... It's the
power of science!
That again, huh?
The power of science
is an amazing thing.
If you keep toying
with them like this,
they're really
going to resent you.
Cadets disliking
their superior...?
O perish the thought.
Where are you?!
Still haven't found
your boyfriend
from your previous life, huh?
B-boyfriend?!
You know, they say
lovers have a connection
and can always
locate each other.
Would you stop?
There's no way that
mangy, smelly beast
could ever be my true love.
Shh!
What is it?
There...
Apollo!
That's for drinking my shake!
You're mine, pal!
Hah!
Come and get me, ya losers!
There's no way you
can hide forever, Apollo!
So just give up now!
No way!
Are you nuts...?!
I've gotta go rescue Baron!
All by yourself...?
Now that's nuts!
Think he's toast?
No... That blast wasn't
meant to kill him,
just knock the wind
out of his sails...
Let's go get him.
Are you convinced
about my bad luck yet?
I am...
But it's going to
take more than that
to prevent me from
getting close to you.
What are you saying?
Life is far too short...
We can't waste time.
Fire!
That's some drop.
Think the Commander's
trying to kill us?
No.
He probably just
thinks a lot like you.
You know,
survival of the fittest.
Separating the
weak from the strong.
That sort of stuff.
Everyone needs a
helping hand now and then.
Only the weak.
Do you think we'll ever be as
strong as the Commander wants?
Well, we're gonna have to be.
If not, we'll never
defeat the Shadow Angels.
Whoa...
Those self-centered cadets
could find their way out,
if only they would learn how
to cooperate with each other.
So that's the goal
of this training...
Teamwork, eh?
Where are we?
It's... so high...
Hold on.
Sirius!
Reika.
He was here just minutes ago...
Yes... I can still feel the
reverberations of the arrows.
He's mine, got it?!
No way. He's mine.
Hey!
So much for your traps!
You really want to
go that badly, do you?
Damn straight...!
Get outta my way!
If that's what
you really want...
Go on then...
But I doubt you'll
get very far by yourself.
Wanna bet?!
It's him!
Reika!
Sirius...
Yahoo!
Vector Luna taking off!
Dammit...! I'd be
in a Vector right now
if I hadn't come back
to save this trap fodder!
Trap fodder?
I'm on my way, Baron...
Turn that thing around, Apollo!
Forget it...!
I'm gonna rescue Baron.
Hey, get real!
You don't even know
where to find him!
Shut up...! I am gonna find
him and I'm gonna do it alone!
Valley City is under attack!
Attention Vectors Luna and Mars!
Harvest Beasts have been
sighted over Valley City!
Abandon your current
course and intercept!
We'll deploy a retrieval force
to deal with Apollo shortly.
Well, you heard him, Pierre.
Roger that.
Mars and Luna, hurry!
Intel reports they've
begun harvesting humans!
They're harvesting humans?!
What happened to
"I'm gonna do it alone?!"
I'm gonna make these
Shadow Angels tell me
where they've took Baron!
Oh, wake up, will you?!
You monsters!
Harvest that.
The leader, huh?
It's gone!
What?!
Silvia! What the--?!
Oh noo!
Their formations
are in total chaos.
Hey, watch it!
No you watch it, moron!
God dammit!
Where are those
blasts coming from?!
Apollo!
Why can't you find that thing?!
I could if you'd shut up!
Hey wait!
Maybe it's hiding
underground somewhere!
Ahh, dammit, this
is getting us nowhere!
They just need to
hurry up and merge!
Negative, sir!
Their auras aren't in sync!
Look at the merge index!
It's too low!
All three... Out of sync...
Apollo!
Silvia hang on!
They're gonna have
to do better than that!
Silvia!
Baron!
Snap out of it!
You're not the only
person who's lost a friend
to the Shadow Angels...
I'd say just about everybody
knows what it feels like
to lose a loved one to those
monsters, myself included.
I didn't know.
There's only one way
to close the gaping
holes in our hearts...
Make ourselves strong
to battle the enemy...!
That's all we can do!
Make ourselves strong...
Multi-dimensional
quantum levels rising.
Look...! Their merge gauges.
They're finally connecting...
...like a jigsaw puzzle!
That's not a bad analogy.
An individual piece doesn't
make much of a difference,
but when all the
pieces come together,
you can solve the puzzle.
I think those three
finally just realized that.
Yes. It is the principle
Aquarion was built on.
They had to learn that they will
never prevail without teamwork.
It's the most important lesson.
That's what it takes
to form a true merge.
Aquarion Mars...!
Initiate Merge!
Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go...! Aquarion!
I'm on fire!
Well, where is it?
Quiet!
Found it!
White Hot... Fire Kick!
Pierre's blood pressure
and pulse are elevated!
Lactic acid levels
have risen as well!
Are you okay...
Guys!
The Harvest Beast
is about to get away!
No!
Change to Solar!
Oh, no, you don't!
Outta my way!
We're too late...
Apollo...
I'll find 'em, I swear!
Baron and all the others!
I will bring them back!
Punch, punch,
punch, punch, punch,
punch, punch, punch...!
Hey, c'mon!
How many times do
I have to say this?
Infinity!
Next time on Aquarion:
"To the Other Side of Emotions."
We're gonna merge
again, aren't we?
Ya' think?!