Made you look!
Futaba...!
Child, what are you doing
playing with that feather again?
It's so much fun...!
This was Apollonius' feather...!
C'mon, let me show
you one of its tricks!
Look at this!
You see?
Would you turn a symbol of our
dark past into a mere toy...?
That boy is so innocent...
When we were his age, we
were too busy helping harvest
for Prana to have
time for idle playing...
Of course, that was long ago.
I doubt the wingless ones will
find Futaba so innocent...
To them, every last
one of us is a threat.
Don't overestimate the child...
He may have a special
control over that feather,
but he has no
place in a harvest.
Don't you think this is a bit
too much food for one person?
Seriously, Apollo, you
look like a disgusting pig.
Shut up...!
I'm not going to stop eating
until I've had my share
and all of theirs, too...!
Just leave me alone.
Who's he talking about?
I think he means all his friends
who were taken away
by the Shadow Angels.
Today's supposed to be some
sort of anniversary for him-
don't know what for, though...
He mentioned something
about it to me this morning.
I'll never forgive
them for taking you.
And I'll always
remember that first day
when you gave me my name.
How is he not freezing.
It's like he's from the sun
Hey, I finally decided
on a name for ya!
A name?
As of today kid,
your name is Apollo...
Just like the
mythological god of the sun!
A- a... po... lo.
Hey guys...!
I hope you're hungry...
'Cause today we hit the jackpot!
You know what I really want...?
I want all of us to be able to
eat our fill every day
of the week for the rest
of our lives like a family.
Look after the
little ones for me!
Baron... I won't let you
down again... I promise.
What perfect timing.
What's going on...?
Why are there so many of them?
Something's not right.
Tough...
'cause I'm really not in
the mood to ask questions...
Now let's Merge!
Merge One!
Go Merge Two!
Go... Aquarion!
Let's go!
It's more powerful than normal!
What...?
A feather?
That sound.
We're the only ones
that can hear it.
Come on...
Unless you'd
rather chat all day!
This is horrible!
All the people in that
city will be killed!
Commander, it
doesn't make sense.
They're not harvesting humans,
they're just laying
waste to the city...
Why are they doing that?
I don't think that
they have a reason.
That's what worries me.
Is this Futaba's mischief?
Yes... He seems to
get a special pleasure
out of toying
with Solar Wing.
Foolish boy...
He treats the harvest
like a child's game.
Let him be. He is a child.
His battles are wasteful...
He can't be allowed to wipe out
our Prana supply on a whim...
The boy needs to learn to
take the harvest seriously.
He's still young...
He has plenty of time to learn.
You have always been
so easy on Futaba, Master.
It would seem the
feather of Apollonius
has found a new
way to torment us...
I tried to talk to him...
The boy should
have listened to me.
Do you understand
why we must harvest
the wingless ones...?
We need them for their Prana.
That's no fun.
How are we supposed
to play with them
if they've got all the
life sucked out of 'em?
I bet the wingless
ones don't like it either.
Not so...
The wingless ones are
merely ignorant and afraid...
But observe how content they are
once they've become
a part of our garden.
Oh, I didn't know that...
I'll bring lots
of 'em here then!
Futaba, wait!
I'll see you later, Shiruha!
Get back here!
What happened?
It just exploded.
Wait... that noise...
Brother, was that-
The feather. But I can't
tell where it's coming from.
Well... Let's find out!
I love fireworks!
Was that a child?
Elements report...
What's happened up there?
A child...!
There was definitely
a child's voice...
Didn't you hear it?
What do you mean...?
We didn't hear anything.
Then Jun, Rena,
figure out what's going on.
Right.
I see innocence...
and I see death...
A massacre without
malice or murderous intent.
I've got it...
It looks like a tiny
hand holding a feather.
What does it mean?
Is that laughter?
Brother... what's
a child doing here?
Stay calm... Just ignore it.
But, how can I?
Quit playing around!
Game over!
Apollo!
What the...? That light...
It's... jumping between
the Cherubim soldiers.
They're toying with us.
Let's aim for the light...
If we get that,
we can stop them all.
Consider it done.
You missed.
I'm getting tired of this.
Look!
Silvia's right...
It is a child... But how
is that even possible?
It doesn't matter...
Let's just get rid of it.
A child? Are you sure?
How old do you think it is?
Clearly too young
to know the difference
between right and wrong...
Commander?
What...? You've finished it...?
You're sure that it's
ready to be tested...?
All right, then begin
preparations for launch.
Sir!
All launch gates standing by...
System ready... All
personnel clear launch area.
We've been perfecting
this system for years...
Failure is not acceptable.
Is that understood?
Yes sir!
Gotcha! Now you're dead...
I won't let you
get away this time.
Apollo, calm down...!
Remember this is just a little
kid you're talking about.
No... I'm talkin' about
a shadow angel.
Just stop... Think
about what you're doing!
I am thinkin'...
about my friends...
About Baron...
And how the shadow angels
just took his life
like it was nothing...
I won't forgive any of them!
Apollo.
Hold on... What is that?
What is what?
Apollo, Sirius, Silvia...
We're going to try to
capture the Shadow Angel.
Huh?
How are we supposed to do that?
Preparing Systems.
Capture Systems one through
six now ready for launch, sir.
All Elements...!
Concentrate your power auras!
The net is in
place for capture...
All Vectors standing by.
What's that thing
supposed to be?
It's the new Quantum
Barrier Field system...
No one can escape once
they've crossed the barrier
and been caught in the net...
Drive the Shadow Angel into
the net but don't hurt him.
I don't think so...!
Those monsters need to suffer!
Apollo... Just let me do this.
Why should I?
Because he may
be a Shadow Angel,
but he's just a kid...
We'll gain nothing
by hurting him.
Hey, come back!
Stop...! This isn't just
some game, you little brat!
No, Apollo...! Let him go...
He's just a kid, he doesn't
understand the difference.
Apollo, you know she's right!
You're wrong...
Kid or not...
he's still one of them...
He knows his kind
hunt down humans!
No!
I've had enough of this!
Apollo!
I'm warning you to stop now!
Shut the hell up!
Catch me if you can!
Calm down... Apollo, you
have to get a grip on yourself!
Please, Apollo! Leave him alone!
Quit saying that!
For the last time,
I don't care...!
How does being a kid
give him the right to kill?
It doesn't...
But we don't have to hurt him...
Can't we at least
try talking to him first?
Talking to him first.
That's something
Baron would have done...
He said kids just
need someone...
teach 'em right from wrong...
No Apollo...! You can't do this!
Be rational for
once in your life!
Give it a rest...!
I'm gonna give this kid
exactly what he needs...
a good talking to...!
Oh no you don't!
Infinity... Slap!
Elements... Transfer your auras!
Barrier field activated!
You did it...!
You got him into the
net without hurting him!
Yeah. Great.
Mission completed.
We have successfully
captured the Shadow Angel.
We'll transfer him now to
the army's Laguna Base
for further investigation.
He's so small.
Look at that...
why is he shivering?
They'll lower his
body temperature
until he enters a state
of suspended animation.
It's easier to handle that way.
Reika...
What'll they do...?
I mean... you don't think
they're going to
kill him, do you?
No, they won't kill him...
at least not right away...
They'll study him for a while,
treat him like a
science experiment...
He's a good specimen,
and there's a lot we
don't know about his kind.
Specimen...
Sounds pretty cold...
He'll spend his life in a box...
His future's
shrouded in darkness.
I'm worried, Brother...
I'm not really sure that
we did the right thing.
Commander... the capture
of the Shadow Angel child
seems to be causing some
uneasiness among the Elements.
Those who look closely
will see that humans
and Shadow Angels are in
may ways, "birds of a feather."
Still... Shadow Angels
believe that we humans
are no better than animals,
that we lack any real
intelligence or emotion.
That's how they can do it...
How they're able
to harvest us...
They've convinced themselves
that a human life is nothing.
They see the harvesting
of humans as we see
the raising of livestock
and the planting of crops.
I know...
We may be no better
than them in the end.
You were the one who captured
the Shadow Angel today, yes?
Yeah, what of it.
You've never captured anyone
before, have you, Apollo...?
You have to see this
through to the end.
You must understand that all
actions have consequences.
I don't like it here!
I'm afraid!
That sound again...!
The angel child...!
Silvia! What is it?
Are you okay?
Reika, listen...!
Can't you hear that noise...?
It's a feather...
There it is again...! The
angel's feather is calling out!
I'm sorry, but
I don't hear anything.
Stop... Stop crying!
I want to go home...!
I'm scared!
He's able to hear
the Shadow Angel, too!
What's the matter?
What... What is this?
No!
He's dead?!
I can smell it...
It's the same...
The same smell as when the
Shadow Angels took Baron.
It's happened again...
The feathers of our kind
falling to the ground.
Master Toma...
The wingless ones
have sealed their fate.
What...?! More special training?
Quit whining!
What, are you afraid
you can't handle it?
Let's see you train with us,
"Deputy Commander."
You're on...!
I'll show you brats
a thing or two...
Next on Aquarion:
"Crimson Path"!