This is all your fault, Apollo!
We had them in our sights
and you just let them get away!
My fault...?
I would've caught 'em
if I wasn't dragging
your dead weight!
Whatever...!
You're always
getting in our way!
What...?!
I'm the one who has
to take responsibility
for your failures...
Just put yourself in my shoes.
Good idea.
We'll start with the shoes
and move upwards,
until you've completely
become each other!
Commander?
What's he mean?
That doesn't sound good.
Ya, no.
Hello...!
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
Why are you dressed
like that, Jun?!
Dressed like what?
And my name isn't Jun.
It's Tsugumi.
Tsugumi Rosenmeier...
Pleased to meet you!
What, the?
Okay guys, Jun's
finally cracked.
Just ignore him.
What are...
What the hell are you doing?!
Please don't yell at me!
I can't take it...!
My heart might explode!
Stopppp!
My melon loaves!
I can't take this.
Tsugumi, are you okay?
This isn't funny, Jun.
It's not a joke, in
order to become someone,
you have to start by
taking on their appearance.
What?!
Oh, no...
Please say you
don't mean Cos Play!
Yup!
I've been into role
playing for years now...
Oh here,
I've got some pictures from my
last sci-fi convention... See!
And we have
costumes for everyone!
Tell me he's joking.
I had the DEAVA uniform
department duplicate
your outfits into
different sizes.
No way.
Silvia and Reika...
Pierre and Chloe...
Apollo and Sirius...
You will each wear
the other's clothes...
And you will wear them
as if they were your own!
What? This isn't fair,
why do I have to be Reika?
This is absurd...!
I'd have to devolve
to imitate that mongrel!
And how can I be you...?
I don't have a stick up my butt.
Come on... Is it that bad?
Yeah! It's that bad.
Couldn't be worse.
I hate to tell you this...
But that means
you're afraid to admit
how much of yourself you
see in the other person.
What?!
She doesn't know
what she's saying...
You're nothing like him.
This sucks.
We already covered
it in basic psychology.
When people detect their own
repressed emotions in another,
they tend to reject that person.
So the person you might
hate or have trouble with
is the person most similar
to the traits you don't
want to see in yourself.
And no matter how much you
don't want to admit it...
You've got a lot in
common with them.
Whaat...?!
So, you're saying that
Reika and I are alike?!
No way.
Just my luck
Why don't you
all quit pretending
that you don't know
what I'm talking about...
Reika, Sirius, Chloe...
Your papers on
unconscious projection
were very well written.
This isn't a
term paper, it's life.
Yes...
And the cold truth of
reality is always harder
to face than the
safety of a theory...
It's time to quit thinking
about the truth...!
And experience it!
Hey, Chloe...
You're always so distant
when I'm around...
Does this mean you actually
wanna get close to me?
I think not.
Well! Let's see
how you really feel!
That's sick.
Pierre...!
I'm always so
standoffish towards you
because I don't like it when
you talk to the other girls...!
From now on, I only want
you to talk to me... 'kay?
Really?
But, sis?
Well it's true...
I'm always so reserved around
Pierre because I'm afraid that
if I open up he might
not actually like me.
Did you... really mean that?
As I said...
We repress our
compassion out of fear.
I'll show you compassion!
Oh, brother...
Don't you like me as
much as you like Reika?
Back off...!
Now you've crossed
the line Pierre.
Brother!
Stop acting like that,
you're scaring me.
You sound just like Apollo.
Pierre!
No fair.
That's exactly
how you treat Apollo.
What?! You stay out of this!
Oh no!
My misfortune.
Do I really sound like that?
You're hiding food from me.
Melon loaves!
Hands off!
That's me.
Sorry, Silvia, guess
we don't have a choice.
What?
Sirius!
Sirius...! Where are you?
Where are you brother...?
Please come back.
Don't leave me alone.
That's so tragic...
What kind of a world would
tear two siblings away
from each other?
Hark, Slyvia.
Let's talk about flowers.
Come...! I'll waste
your time with a poem!
Brother?
There you are!
Oh, thank goodness,
I've been looking everywhere!
I found you!
Hands off!
Stay away from him,
your brother's over there!
You're breaking character!
Okay, look Reika...
If you can so easily
pretend to be me,
then you can pretend
that he's your brother!
Come... beloved sister!
Uh, right. Sorry.
Oh brother!
Stop it!
What?
Huh? Ah, I...
Silvia doesn't
want us to see it...
But she can't hide the fact
that she's in love with Apollo,
although she's too scared
to reincarnate their passion.
Oh please no...
Don't be cruel, Pierre...!
You shouldn't tease them
with the truth like that.
What do you mean the truth?
Please stop.
See what you've done?
Yeah.
Y-you've got it all wrong,
Silvia just got confused
and she thought I was Sirius!
Oh, sweet rose.
Your fragrance stirs my soul.
I crave your soft touch...
...and hunger for you.
Brother!
When was the last time
you looked into a mirror?
What're you all lookin' at...?
This costume crap's easy...
Just ask the little prince here.
You can wear the clothes,
but you still smell
like a mongrel to me.
How revolting.
Very convincing.
Convincingly pathetic.
Rena...?! You can walk!
You've mimicked
words and appearances
to create a mockery
of each other,
but inside nothing has changed.
It's you! But when- ?
From the very start.
Then where's Rena?
In the infirmary with Anemia...
As usual.
Look, old man...
Just cause you're magic doesn't
mean we're doing it wrong.
This frog knows itself...
It doesn't have to try because
it already knows what it is!
What?
Sirius... it's getting late.
A frog doesn't try because
it knows what it is...
How can I become
something without trying?
You wanna be like Apollo?
You could start
by catching that frog...
...and then eating it alive.
He eats... frogs?
That's disgusting!
He doesn't just eat frogs.
He once told me that he hunts
for animals in the woods
behind DEAVA headquarters.
Then he can't resist
his primal instincts.
He tracks the animals
by their scent.
By scent...? Interesting.
Wait, where are you going?
I'm going hunting...
It's the only way
to become Apollo.
He can't mean that.
I'm afraid he does...
They can imitate
outward emotion...
But they can't seem to
see beyond the surface...
I think it's still
too early for them
to recognize the common
darkness within them.
Children always grow up
faster than their
parents expect them to.
They're on the verge of
understanding the truth
of the three arrows and
harnessing their strength.
I don't mean to
question you, Commander,
but I'm just a
little confused...
When you told us that story,
I thought the whole point was
that even three arrows together
could still be broken...
There's no weakness
when each arrow understands
the strength of the others.
Only through
their collective power
will they realize
their full potential.
Their full potential?
Sirius.
Mama, nooo! Father, please!
Where's mama!
Reika...? What's wrong?
No, please! Brother!
Don't leave me like this!
Come back! Sirius!
Please don't go!
Is that... supposed to be me?
Brother!
Don't leave me alone.
Man, how stuffy
can a dorm room get?
It smells like an antique store.
Well that smells odd.
What is it?
Reika's bad luck
must be rubbing off.
Jeez, does Reika
always have it this bad?
Sirius...?
You've gone so far
to become Apollo...
I can't stop until
I've become Reika.
If you've chosen to
suffer, then so will I.
How does he do endure this?
Flowers.
It smells so nice.
Something's on fire!
Not them.
Everything burned to the ground.
Not now!
That is just my luck.
No, I can't go without brother!
This is absurd.
Yeah! I can smell them nearby!
I'm scared...
Something is wrong.
Like what?
What is that?
What the hell is that!
They look exactly like us...!
I've confirmed their
quantum patterns...!
They're perfect copies...
From their size right down to
their energy output signatures!
Look at that...!
It's like a mirror image!
How cheap can they get?
Vector Sol to all Units...
Initiate formation, S L M...
Call it codename,
Beautiful Shape.
Roger!
Okay, let's do it!
Hot damn!
Awesome...!
They're still in character
without even wearing
their costumes!
Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go, Aquarion!
What happened?!
Merge failed!.
Their Third Emotional
Merge Level potential
is nowhere close to sufficient!
But that level
registers the soul.
The third emotional
level is vital.
Harvest Beasts approaching!
Look!
The enemy is merging!
That can't be...!
How can the Shadow Angels
form Aquarion?!
Why of course!
They've analyzed and replicated
our Merge formations
from other encounters.
What's going on...?!
Why can't we merge?!
Brother.
What's stopping us?
Once a frog, always a frog...
Once a hawk, always a hawk...
Once a wolf, always a wolf.
But, sir.
Those are just words.
Quit speaking in
riddles, old man.
We've already become each other.
Bastards!
They won't stop mimicking us!
Mimic.
I can mimic all I want!
But I'll always be me!
You're right,
I can only be me...!
And I accept that!
That was well put, Silvia...
You are indeed my sister.
Yes, and you're my brother!
The Third Emotional Levels
have reached full capacity!
Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go, Aquarion!
This merge, it's different.
It's incredible!
I feel like I'm melting!
They did it!
It's radiating!
The time has come.
Hey, copycat...!
Can you do this?!
Aquarion!
It's growing!
How is that possible?!
Solar diagnostic.
Quantum energy
levels increasing...!
It seems to be
drawing mass from within!
But how?
I've never seen
anything like this.
Three arrows pointed in the
same direction are useless...
They're easily broken!
But if they choose
their own course
and respect each other's path...
If they appreciate their
individual strengths,
they will help each other grow.
But if each arrow faces off
in their own random direction...
Won't they be rendered useless?
Of course, if the
directions were random...
Although... if they're
able to find a connection
in each other's weaknesses,
they will soon
recognize their strengths.
Once they've made this
connection
and they're finally able
to become themselves,
they'll be free to become
one with each other.
The sign of the Vectors!
I can't believe it!
When the three
Vectors join souls
and extend from the
center of this bond,
they create harmony...
They become perfectly aligned
with the solar system...
And once they've
managed to do this...
They will transcend
the third dimension...
Transcend your configuration
and join as one...
Become a single giant shape!
Mimic that.
The power within
us can never be
duplicated through
pale imitation.
Let's do it!
United...
Trans-dimensional...
Attack!
They found their true selves.
By seeing through
one another's eyes.
Commander...
If they had to reject each
other to discover that,
how were they able to connect?
Oh look... It's just so perfect.
Circle... Circle...
Up, down, I can't figure it out.
What does it mean?!
Jerome, you're
thinking too much.
That isn't an unsolved
code, it's just graffiti.
Graffiti?!
Next time:
"Mischief Without Malice."