I love being alive...!
I love it all!
Tsugumi... are you alright?
Military vectors.
So, they just used us to
break through the barriers.
Silvia's up there.
We can't let'em
get through. Not now.
What?
Tsugumi!
Tsugumi will switch with Pierre.
You've got it!
Don't worry, Chloe.
We'll get you better, I promise.
Get me up there!
Go!
Right.
Prepared for Operation
Blackout... Confirm.
Yes sir.
How many vectors
do we have left?
Nine, sir.
All vectors assume
Armageddon Formation.
What the-
Target is at twelve o'clock...
Set PSG cannons to maximum fire.
Roger.
Fire!
What was that?
Damn!
Cursed wingless ones!
Give up your pathetic fight...
You won't get any further!
Omega change.
Child's play!
Glen!
Worthless creature!
No!
I'm sorry...
It's you.
Remember
Reika!
Now you die!
Reika.
You're back!
You're alright...?
Does this mean you're
back to normal?!
Yeah... It's me.
Sorry if I scared ya.
You're finished!
Glen!
You go on. I've got this.
I won't leave you!
You don't have a choice!
Yes I do, and I'm not
leaving you behind!
Dammit, there's
no time to argue.
But-
This is bigger than the two of
us, Reika, and you know it!
All right.
Let's go!
Why won't you die!
Thanks, Glen...
Apollo, Pierre...
let's get moving!
Right behind you.
According to prophecy,
when Solar Wing
returns to Heaven...
Then the world...
will come to an end.
Do they have a hope of winning?
Winning?
Will they be able to
destroy the Shadow Angels?
Where the hell are we?
It's their garden...!
Those are the
people taken for Prana
by the Shadow Angels
during their harvests.
Are you kidding me?
If that's true, if that's really
who those people are,
do you think everyone
the Shadow Angels
have ever taken away is
still down there somewhere?
The fate of the Shadow
Angels' is linked to ours...
They use humans... but they
also need us to survive...
They cannot afford
to destroy us.
Even so, we'll be slaves!
We will...
If the Shadow Angels
Prevail we'll live
but we won't be free...
our lives will be cheap...
Dammit, this is taking
way too much time.
We got to get to Silvia.
Let's go!
It's huge!
That's it...!
That has to be the Tree of Life.
Can you guys smell that?
What is it?
It's... like nothing
I've ever smelled before...
Whatever it is,
it's really powerful.
Powerful?
What do you think is up there?
They must not topple
the Tree of Life...
The tree contains the
life-force of the entire planet,
and controls its fate...
They cannot let
that force loose...
If the tree falls and
the energy escapes,
this will be a
lifeless planet forever.
Is that really possible?
You won't get away!
We'll see.
Is that really the
best you can do?
Wingless fools...
You can't even
put up a good fight.
Bastard! This isn't over yet.
Hear me! It's not over!
What is this?
What are you doing?
Your kind will never win.
No! Glen!
No, please! Glen!!!
How is it that you have
the answer to everything...?
Twelve thousand years ago,
we defeated the Shadow Angels...
There were only three
Elements in that battle:
Apollonius, Seliane,
and one Element whose name
has been erased from
the Book of Genesis.
You were the third, weren't you?
Apollonius!
Seliane!
Where am I?
Sirius!
Welcome home.
Brother!
Wait a second.
Is this place...
What I think it is?
Yes... You are in Atlandia now.
But this place belongs
to the Shadow Angels!
There really are
angels, Silvia...
Look around and you'll see it...
Their city is beautiful.
No, it's not.
You've at least remembered parts
of your past life as Seliane...
I envy you that.
I haven't seen
anything of mine...
But I know the
memory's inside of me...
I need to find it, Silvia, so I
can figure out who I really am.
That's why I needed to
come here to Atlandia...
And why it's so important
for you to stand by my side.
You're wrong...
You're so blind...
But I'll make you see!
You can watch from
a nice, safe place
while we put an end
to the wingless ones.
Wow.
The Tree of Life.
It looks exactly like
it did in my dream...
It's so big,
but so fragile too...
I hope it stays safe.
That's Vector Sol...!
Apollo! Apollo, is that you?
That's her scent...! Silvia!
Sirius?!
Where have you been...?
You're late.
Angel attack... Go Mars!
Uh-oh... Sirius merged himself
with the Cherubim again.
Reika...!
Whatever you have to do,
you can't let go of his hand.
No, for Glen's sake,
I won't... Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go! Aquarion!
Sirius!!!
No!
You can't... please stop!
Reika!
Right!
Let it go, Sirius. It's over.
He's right...
Please listen. You have to stop!
Cherubim Mars and Solar Aquarion
seem to be equal in
strength and agility...
This won't be short.
There seems to be a
strange reaction occurring
between the machines.
Well... They should
have company soon.
I can't see. What the hell???
Hello Solar Wing.
I've waited ages
for this day to come
Nice try, but you missed!
What the hell?
I never miss.
Apollo!
What...!
The controls won't work.
We can't do anything from here.
Don't you remember, Apollonius?
Think back to twelve
thousand years ago.
Even in this new body, you
must remember who you were.
Have you forgotten the
feel of my hand in yours.
You cannot have forgotten
how I loved you...
We were twin souls.
Apollonius?
What was that...? Why is
that memory in my head?
You will remember...! You will!
Yes, I do remember...
I remember your
hands, your face,
loving you
so much it hurt.
I remember it all.
You do?
Seliane!
Apollonius!
Even now, you can't
abandon her memory,
even though she was nothing...
You knew her then, Apollonius,
and in your ignorance,
you feel you know her now.
But you don't
know her true form.
What do you mean?
Silvia?
Seliane...
Being weak, your sin was far
too great to bear alone...
So naturally, your soul divided.
One half became you, and
the other became your brother.
Haven't you wondered why
you both have one winged arm.
No...! This is ridiculous!
I can't be her!
The proof is on your arms...
Seliane's soul split in two:
one half that remembered,
and one that forgot.
The half that remembered
the world's destruction
became the
haunted older brother.
The one that forgot
became the carefree sister.
No! He's wrong!
But I don't remember!
Your mind doesn't...
It could never
handle the knowledge
of who you really are...
But your soul knows the truth.
You're lying...
I'm the reincarnation of
Apollonius, not Seliane...!
Do you hear me, I am Solar Wing!
You, Solar Wing?
You truly know nothing...
Solar Wing is neither
angel nor human,
but something far greater...
Solar Wing is Aquarion!
But how?
That doesn't make sense!
You got to be kidding me!
Twelve thousand years ago,
Apollonius betrayed me...
He betrayed our whole race
for his love, Seliane...
He left Atlandia
behind him forever...
but he didn't vanish...
He reappeared clothed in a
form I did not recognize...
He was born into the
land of the wingless ones
as Aquarion, the Solar Wing...
And as Solar Wing,
he mercilessly
destroyed our home...
As if he had never
known its heavenly light...
And now...
Now what?
And now you will
pay for that betrayal...
You'll know what it means
to lose the one you
love, just as I did...
You do still love
Seliane, do you not...?
Don't!
But that's my sister...!
You can't do this!
Time to die, Seliane.
Seliane, no!
Be careful.
I am not as weak
as you think I am...
Remember... I am heir to
the legacy of Apollonius...
I'm not Seliane.
I am Silvia of de Alisia!
Brother, no!
It's over.
Master Toma!
Now it's your turn
to say goodbye.
Toma!
Brother!
Sirius!
The Tree of Life has
grown heavy, burdened
with the fruit that will
bring forth a new world...
Watch closely and
listen well, wingless ones.
Next on Aquarion...
the final episode...
"The Day the World Begins."