Hey, Chloe...
What was it like the other day?
Huh?
Yeah, wasn't it
your first Merge?
Her first?
Come on, what was it like?
Yeah. Chloe, please tell us!
Ok I heard that
everyone's nervous
the first time they Merge?
Is that true?
Oh my gosh!
Was it really amazing?
Well, it was... I don't
know how to describe it.
No, I can't...
Why don't you try
asking Silvia instead?
She's more
experienced than I am.
Really...? It's always
that incredible?
It doesn't matter
who you do it with...?
What if it's Apollo?
It's the same, even
with an animal like him.
You know, I don't really
mind not being a pilot.
How can you say that, Jun...?
You and I are the only
ones who haven't Merged...!
Don't you think
it's embarrassing?
Not really.
It's enough for me just to be
around these amazing machines.
That's all the rush I need.
Hey, idiots!
Get back to work or you'll find
yourself scrubbing the johns!
Yes sir!
You really want
to go into battle?
Yeah, why not?
Why not...?
Aquarion's dangerous...
You've seen
those fights before...
You could get hurt, or even die.
I know all that...
I know it's dangerous.
But still...
Still what?
Well... it's just...
I really want to know what
it would be like to
Merge, that's all.
That's it?
They say that it's the
best feeling in the world.
Hey, Reika.
You want some coffee...?
It's the weak stuff
from the cafeteria,
but still, it's
better than nothing.
I can't...
Everyone's better off
if I just stay by myself.
Oooo!
You know... it's after curfew.
Reika! I'm sorry I'm late.
It won't happen again!
Reika...
There's something
I wanted to ask you.
'Kay, what is it?
Well... um... it's just...
What was it like the
first time you Merged?
Were you scared?
Did it feel good?
So that's what
this is all about...
The first time?
Yeah, well,
I heard it feels good.
They grow up so soon!
How do I explain this?
Well... for one thing,
the first time isn't
the same for anyone.
Okay...
But Silvia said it feels great
no matter who you're with.
Oh... well...
Silvia said that, did she?
It's important
not to be selfish.
Remember you're not
the only one involved...
Your feelings
are only part of it.
Right... I'm only part of it...
Gotcha, what else
do I need to know?
Remember the other
people in the Merge.
You have to be
in sync with them.
In sync... I can do that.
Alright...
But it isn't enough
just to remain in sync.
Uh-huh.
Nope...
You have to take control
when the time comes...
You have to be firm.
Firm... Like this?
No, no, no.
You don't quite have it.
See... That's more
like what I meant.
Sometimes your Merge
partners may get carried away.
But you have to remember to
stay in control of yourself.
Okay, but how do you do that?
It's like I told you before.
Remain calm and
remember to breathe...
I'm sorry Tsugumi,
is any of this helpful?
Oh yes...! You've
been a huge help!
You're so easy to talk to.
Oh... You mean it?
Yeah... You're great!
No... No...!
Nooooo!
Vector Luna reporting.
I'm- I'm prepared
to Merge... I think.
Just try to relax, Tsugumi.
We're going to get through this.
I'm not sure I can...
I'm nervous.
We all are the first time.
Alright.
Vector Mars standing
by for Merge.
Here we go!
Okay. Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go... Aquarion!
Oh wow...! We Merged!
I forgot, the stupid simulator
doesn't go all the way.
You did well.
Thanks. I tried really hard.
You seemed to
relax as time passed.
That's good.
Well, yeah...
But it took awhile.
Just keep trying.
Reika?
Sorry about that, Tsugumi.
Are you alright?
What's that?
What the heck's happening...?
Where'd all that rumbling
come from just now?
Another explosion...?
What's going on around here?
They're trying to find
the source of it right now.
I want to know what happened!
Brother, didn't this same thing
happen a little while ago?
Yes.
Anybody know what that was?
Huh? What is this?
Hey you guys, look!
There's something pulsing.
What are we looking at?
What's this image from?
It's Jun's psychograph.
That thing--it
looks like a heart.
I don't know about you,
but I can never tell
what those weird pictures
are supposed to be.
Whatever it is, it's going
faster than it was before.
Tsugumi!
Where'd it go?
It's another explosion...!
Everybody take cover!
It's Tsugumi again!
Tsugumi! Tsugumi!
That girl's a danger!
Nobody's safe when she's around
Make them stop!
I can't Merge;
nobody's safe around me!
Cherubim soldiers
sighted in Mira City.
Model unknown.
Vector Sol, Apollo.
Vector Mars, Jun Lee.
Vector Luna, Tsugumi Rosenmeir.
Report to flight deck and
prepare for launch immediately.
I can't go...!
Someone else has to do it!
I can't; I can't go!
Time to move out!
I can't go. Please understand!
I can't do anything to help!
So you plan to sit here and
let the others do the fighting?
Will you always be running away?
Suit yourself.
I suppose it had
to happen sometime.
Where's Tsugumi?
She's going to miss the launch.
What's that girl up to?
This is no time for
a disappearing act!
I'll volunteer to go
in her place, sir!
Of course.
Remember, I'm the head Element!
Fine by me.
I'm just happy that I'm going
to be seeing some action...
Don't worry, Reika, I'm sure
I'll do just as well as Tsugumi.
Well... I guess there's
really no other way.
Prepare to launch with Pierre as
Vector Luna instead of Tsugumi.
Tsugumi.
Launch gates
standing by for take-off.
Launch gates standing by.
Clear launch area.
Secure hangers.
All non-flight personnel
evacuate flight deck.
Repeat: all non-flight
personnel evacuate flight deck
and report to observation deck.
All vectors in place...
Initiating launch sequence.
Just don't get in
my way, Rookie...
Got that?
Uh, yeah... r-right.
Just remember everything
we talked about, Jun.
And don't take
Apollo too seriously.
Well, this should be
interesting, at least.
Vector status,
twenty seconds to arrival.
Prepare to acquire target.
Roger. Quantum
reactor initiated.
Target sighted.
Let's go.
Uh... yes!
Right...! Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go...! Aquarion!
Oh wow.
Even better than I'd heard.
So Jun got to Merge...
I'm glad.
Here it goes guys!
Infinity Punch!
What...?
Are you sure you want
to use that one now?!
What happened?
It always works!
Apollo, give me a shot at 'em.
I think I can
heat things up a bit.
Good idea!
Alright... Let's go.
I'm ready.
Fire!
Punch!
New model has a harder
shell than the others.
I noticed.
It looks as if it may have
an impenetrable suit of armor.
We need to change our tactics.
Ah, You think?!
Aquarion's been hit.
Pierre!
Pierre...! Answer me!
Pierre's pulse is barely
registering, Jerome.
He may die.
This is why I wanted
Tsugumi for this mission...!
She can't hide forever...
Changing Element!
Vector Luna from Pierre
to Tsugumi Rosenmeier.
No...! No!
No, wait!
Let me go instead.
I'll take Tsugumi's place.
Tsugumi has to fly sometime.
And, in my opinion, she's
better suited to this mission.
As her senior,
I assume responsibility.
Reika.
Very well. Begin
preparations for teleport.
Teleport standing by.
Initiating teleport switch.
Medical team, move in now!
Measure his pulse
and blood pressure...
There may be brain damage,
so perform a CT scan as well.
And be careful!
Reika will be fine...
It's better for everyone
if I just stay here.
Vector Luna in...
Teleport switch complete.
Alright then...
Let's get moving.
I'm coming! Wait for me!
Guys, we need to
Merge--and soon!
We know that!
Look out!
Reika's been hit!
I repeat! Reika's hit!
Vector Luna, come in!
Reika!
Are you okay, Reika?
Just barely.
Vector Luna's stats are falling.
Aura level nearing zero.
Energy at fifty percent.
Mental capacity fading.
We can't get past its armor...
None of our usual
attacks are going to
work with this thing...!
We have to think of
something quick or we're toast.
Jun, what're you doing?!
My chest it... it... feels like
my heart's gonna explode.
Wait... That's it!
It's Tsugumi!
Hey, Tsugumi!
We need you!
We need what you can do...
You have to switch places
with Reika immediately.
We don't have
any time to lose...!
Come on Tsugumi,
you can do this.
You have to do this!
They need me?
Tsugumi, hurry!
It has to have a
weakness somewhere.
I'll be fine; I can do this...
Now let's just Merge!
I'm sorry, Reika...
but it has to be Tsugumi.
Reika.
Tsugumi Rosenmeier
reporting for duty.
Standing by for teleport switch.
What...?
Well look who showed up?
Tsugumi.
Hey everybody.
I'm sorry I'm late, but I'm
here now and I'm ready to go.
Hey Tsugumi.
Thanks for getting me here, Jun.
No problem...
But right now, we need you
to send your power
inside that soldier.
You know?
How'd you find out?
I figured it out earlier
from my psychograph...
I get it...
Your heart rate sets
off some kind of reaction.
Right.
It affects the stability
of objects in the vicinity.
We can't beat that
soldier from the outside,
so we have to destroy
it from the inside.
I'll use my psychograph
to guide you.
Hey...! What's going on?
There's no time to
explain that right now...
Get ready to Merge.
OK... whatever it is you're
up to it better be good!
Alright, Tsugumi, let's go.
Formation is L-S-M...
Codename "Explosion."
Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go... Aquarion!
Oh my gosh...
This is incredible!
Aquarion Luna.
This is strange.
Vector Luna's energy level
is higher than I've
ever seen before.
No!
Jun I can't... make it stop!
Tsugumi, hold
on a little longer.
How?
Apollo, get us moving!
What...? To where?
Just run!
Alright.
I can't. I can't.
Remember to stay
in control of yourself.
Right.
Tsugumi...
Remember what I said, please.
Here goes nothing.
Now...
It's time for... an explosion!
Let's go.
What?
So this is why
they needed Tsugumi.
To Merge is... to explode!
I really did it.
You are getting sleepy...
Very sleepy...
You are drifting into
the world of dreams...
You are getting sleepy...
Very sleepy.
Next on Aquarion:
"The Path to Dreams."
Now... you are mine.