Atlandia... The
kingdom of splendor.
Where fragrant breezes...
whisper through the trees.
Where fairies sing
pure and clear.
Where beautiful flowers...
guild upon the grounds.
Where the crisp sound of
bells cast from human souls
echo beautifully off
the walls of history.
Marking an era of
glorious rebirth,
where the old world
would be renewed
from the ash of mankind...
It seems you've quickly
become accustomed to this place.
Yes... It feels as if I've been
here since the day I was born.
You were born here.
This is your home.
In distant times past...
and now again...
Solar Wing...?
Then am I the one?
No! Brother! How could you?!
Welcome home...
Here in Atlandia your
wings will finally bloom.
Master Johannes...
I fear something unholy
has entered our sanctuary.
Calm yourself... Toma knows
exactly what he's doing.
The humans have
taken our only child.
Leaving us only one
chance of survival...
We must hope now
that the sacred Tree of
Life will self-pollinate,
that it will bear a
single Genesis fruit
and spawn a new life...
...before it completely
withers and dies...
That day, I fear...
is very close-at-hand.
Brother...
This is his handwriting...!
The elephant dances.
The elephant dances
an elegant tango.
The elephant spins and it
goes round and round and round
until it forgets... the
weight of the world on its back.
What is this...?!
Brother...
Silvia... I'm so sorry...
I know you must-
Get away from me!
Sophia, have you seen
the Commander?!
No...? Do you need
him for something?
I just received a
message from our superiors,
if we don't recover that
stolen Vector immediately...
Your Mighty Commander Fudo
will be stripped of his post.
So sad... already the
roses wither and die...
Their master gone...
So does this mean...
Apollo wasn't
Solar Wing after all ?
Honestly, I hadn't
thought about it.
Either way, Sirius was
the one the angels took...
I feel so sorry for Silvia...
He was her brother.
Just stop it!
Everybody's been
looking for you.
I'm just taking a small
break from life's rigors.
Actually, I could use
a little break myself.
You know, I've
never figured it out...
Why DEAVA built a base
inside the monastery of
the Alisian royal family...
And why members
of the royal family
would then agree to stay...
Those wristbands...
I've always sensed that
the answer had something
to do with what
they were hiding...
What is this?
You should follow me...
If, that is, you're prepared
to know the truth.
You don't smell very happy.
Well that's because I'm not...!
How could I possibly
be happy right now?
First Glen and now Sirius...
Both of them are gone
and it's all because of me...
That's a bunch of
crap and you know it...
It was the feathers.
Sirius did this cause
he was ashamed of himself.
You mean to tell me
you knew what Sirius
was hiding under his
wristband all along?
Well... yeah... I guess so...
And it didn't bother you?!
You didn't think it might be
important to let someone know?!
What...? Guess I didn't think
it was all that big of a deal...
If I had known...
If I'd had time to react...
I might have made
a different choice.
I might have taken Sirius'
hand when I had the chance...
But I didn't. I couldn't
find it in my heart...
Let's go...
You're coming with me.
Apollo?!
Look around...
This is what we
overthrew the royal family
to get our hands on...
Once the capital of
humanity... Shangri-la.
Shangri-la... The eternal city.
But, these... It takes a century
for stalactites to grow
just one centimeter...
So for these to have
become this thick,
it must have
taken at least...
Twelve thousand years.
Twelve thousand.
Amazing.
Is that...?
A monument to its builders...
Apollonius and Celiane.
It was in this place...
that humans first discovered
a way of combating
the Shadow Angels...
Many innovative technologies
were developed here...
And as legend would have it...
Both human-like Shadow Angels
and Angel-like humans were born.
Securing this
location was paramount,
without it Aquarion
would be inoperable.
In the strata just
beneath these ruins
rests an incredible
source of power.
And that was reason enough
for the royal family
to be overthrown.
Their wristbands were
concealing something...
Shadow Angel feathers.
Silvia and Sirius...
Both are descendants
of Apollonius and Celiane,
whose love for one another was
forbidden, and would eventually
result in the ancient battle
that destroyed the world.
But how could that be?
What was two souls...
became one.
That single soul
became two once more
and from them came a third
soul, the soul of Aquarion.
Why'd you bring me out here?
I don't know...
Cause' it's pretty...
and the smells are nice.
Delicious.
Old man Fudo once said...
"Even if a spring
is never discovered,
it still continues to flow"...
Whatever that means, right?
Apollo?!
Silvia.
Sirius?
Silvia... Please...
Trust me... it's better here.
But Brother?
Silvia no!
Did she reject your offer?
Not at all.
We were just
rudely interrupted...
She'll follow me.
Was he here?!
Was Sirius here?!
You can't!
Silvia, don't go!
Apollo?
How can you be certain
he won't betray you...?
You mean as Apollonius did?
He will not stray from me...
He inherits the Angels' wings
and believes he is
fulfilling his destiny
Even so, he only partially
shares our bloodline--
he is still human as well!
Enough.
The time has come
for your first battle...
Are you truly prepared
to face your former friends?
Friends, they may be...
But not mine...
I've been alone, until now...
Sir?
Your Vector...
Can you fly?
Sir, are you ordering
me on this mission?
Then I promise...
I won't let go
of his hand again!
Go then... You know what to do.
Quantum signature approaching...
Barrier field raised...!
Mount defenses!
High-level quantum
signature confirmed.
Wait is that...?
It's Vector Mars!
So what are you saying...
Then is that Sirius?
It's my brother...?!
Is he coming back home?
I can't tell...
is it really him?
All I know, if he's in there...
I'm bringing him back.
Sirius... Stop this...!
Is that you?!
Reika...! Come back!
Reika!
Sirius, listen!
You don't have to forgive me...
what I did was awful...
I betrayed you and I'm sorry.
But please...
You can't stop trusting
everyone because of my mistake!
Please Sirius...!
Please come home,
I'm begging you!
Sirius!
You said trust...? In whom?
Reika!
Reika... Bastard.
How could you hurt a friend?
Now, mongrel...
Let's go...! Angelic Merge!
Cherubim... Mars!
Sirius!!!!
Vector Mars has just
successfully merged
with a Cherubim!
This isn't happening...
Oh no...
Three seconds.
That's all I'll need...
to finish this.
Three seconds huh...?
Then bring it ooooon!
Okay... One.
Two.
Three.
Apollo!
C'mon...
Everything's busted,
I can't move an inch!
Commander...!
He's anticipating
every move we make!
Now sit there and watch as
I completely destroy DEAVA.
Vectors Sol and Luna
have been incapacitated!
The enemy is right on top of us!
Defense Systems...
Overloading...!
Code red...!
Vector Mars' energy vibrations
are weakening the
Barrier shields!
It won't be long
'til he breaks through!
Oh no!
Make it stop. Please Brother!
There may be nothing
we can do but pray.
Unknown objects approaching...
at high speeds!
What are their stats?
I can not get a reading!
What's this?
What is that?!
Could it be...?
It almost looks like...
Aquarion!
Stay calm... We're all safe now.
You are looking at
the lastest in weaponry
developed jointly by DEAVA
and the New United Nations.
The new Assault-Type Aquarion!
Silvia... and the
rest of you as well.
Behold what humans did to Angels
and what you've done to
those you called friends?
Feathers? What the hell?
What's that...? It's Glen!
Is it really you ?!
It's finally happened...
Humans have crossed
the point of no return,
harnessing forbidden
technologies...
Is it too late for this
travesty to be stopped?
Next on Aquarion:
"Fleeting Wings"
Merge with me!
Merge with me!!