Brother!
Sirius!
How could you... do this?
Did you actually think
I'd ever trust someone
born to the wingless ones?
Yes, that's it.
Merge form Genesis!
Go... Aquarion!
Brother... you're alright!
What's happening...?
My wounds are closing.
Is Aquarion healing me?
I can't believe it. He's alive.
Sirius!
Hey, you alright?
I'm fine... for now...
But I don't blame
you if you both wish
that Toma had killed me.
You're still one of us!
Just be glad you're alive!
Right.
Welcome back, Solar Wing...
Let this be our final battle?
Hell yeah! Let's go!
Look out! Reika!
Right!
He's fast.
He's just playing with us!
Damn it... What?
Chibiko!
Isn't she the one you
were trying to rescue?
Apollo, look after
the little ones for me!
Chibiko!
Chibiko...? Oh, her!
Chibiko...! Maji!
Giving up so soon?
Never! You stole
my friends' lives!
Apollo... hold on.
Let me help you beat him.
Thank you...
Glad you're back.
This should be fun.
Time to die!
We'll see.
Finally... It's
happening at last.
This is the true
light of Solar Wing
as it should have
been centuries ago.
They don't realize it, but their
struggle will restore our power.
After all these
years of waiting,
at last, Solar Wing will
do what we cannot...
The Tree of Life will bear the
fruit of a hundred generations.
We must go to the
Tree of Life, Master.
Yes...
These bodies
are old and tired...
We will offer them to the Tree
and we will be
reborn with the world.
To the Tree of Life!
What's happening?
Look...! Look at the Tree!
Watch out!
It's perfect.
At last our time has come.
How can this be happening...?
The light of Solar Wing
touched the Tree...
Everything is in place!
It's dying when it
should be bearing fruit...
I don't understand...!
It can't die...!
We've waited too long for this!
No!
You're finished!
Toma!
Why bother to kill me...
The world will end soon enough.
What are you talking about?
Do you know nothing...?
The roots of the
Tree of Life reach down
into the very
core of our planet.
The Tree is going to die
and when it does...
the crumbling of its roots
will tear the Earth to pieces...
All life will be destroyed.
What?!
He's wrong!
Look at the Tree!
I'm detecting some
movement at the Earth's core!
Movement is escalating through
every stratum.
If this keeps up, the earth's
crust will begin to shift.
But how?
Something's happened
to the Tree of Life...
It must be collapsing.
Then the world
will collapse with it.
It's over.
No!
Apollo, killing him
isn't the answer.
He's one of them.
He deserves to die.
You can't.
Think this through.
Apollonius! That scent!
A Shadow Angel!
That was Toma's scent.
That's it...
We need a Shadow Angel on board.
Without one of them,
Aquarion's power isn't complete.
We need Toma...
Enemy or not, he's the
only one who can help us.
You children truly know
nothing of the past...
Think of the name: Solar Wing...
It cannot awaken without
the presence of angels.
Reika!
Teleport detected
in Vector Luna!
But who's trying to teleport?
It looks like a Shadow Angel.
Where'd Reika go?
Rieka! Reika!
Toma!
I should have let the kid kill
you when he had the chance.
Now I'll do it for him instead.
Pitiful Wingless One...
I shall not die by your hand.
My legacy will be greater.
If I must sacrifice
my life to restore
the Shadow Angels
to power, then so be it.
I will become Solar Wing!
Are you alright?
Yeah...
I'll be fine.
Toma!
Apollo...! I have to go.
Silvia!
Apollo!
What are you doing?
Please don't go after them!
I have to help...
You heard Toma.
The world's falling apart.
Then let me come too...
Please, don't leave
me behind like this.
No. I need you to stay here and
protect Chibiko and the others!
I swore to Baron
I would rescue them...
Please help me
keep that promise.
No, wait!
Apollo!
I should have killed you
twelve thousand years ago!
That's right, wingless ones.
Just follow me. Genesis merge!
No! Over my dead body!
No way you're going to be
the Head Element, you bastard!
Your kind stole
my friends' lives...
Now back down!
You're nothing
but wingless filth!
You betrayed me!
It appears all three
Vectors are trying
to become the Head Element.
Their aura levels
are out of range.
If they keep that up, they're
going to self destruct.
Distortions in the Earth's
strata are increasing.
The movements are becoming
more severe every minute...
The Earth's crust
can't take much more.
Get away from me...
How do you like that?
Pierre!
You okay, Silvia?
Yeah, I'm alright...
just my arm.
I'm glad...
Nice wing by the way.
Thank you.
It's back up!
That's it.
I'll use that Vector.
Let's go!
Look out!
You've got to be kidding me!
Pierre!
Reika!
That was too close.
I'm going. They need help.
Rena?!
What're you doing here?
I thought you could
use some help,
but the teleport switch threw
me off just a little bit.
Let's go take care of this...
I couldn't agree more...
Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go... Aquarion!
This is amazing!
Aquarion Alpha!
It's almost too easy.
Good luck, you guys.
Apollo... Brother.
Fire Kick!
I may die, but I'm
taking you with me.
Change formation!
This is horrible.
They have to stop fighting!
How pathetic.
Commander?
Just look at them.
Can't you see
their blind hatred...?
Born centuries ago when Seliane
and Apollonius fell in love...
Look what they've done!
And now, the world
is dying again.
I'm so sorry...
I am... But that day,
when I first met Apollonius,
nothing seemed to
exist but the two of us.
And I knew that,
whatever else changed,
I would always love him.
Even if... the world
comes to an end.
Even then-
I will never regret that love...
Tell me, Silvia, when
you place your hands
together like this, what
is left between them?
Right and left...
Angel, human...
When you place them
together, what do you see?
Find what exists
in between, Silvia!
Commander?
Do you see now...?
It's over... You're
no match for an Angel.
What now?
Just hold on...
I'm going to see if I can
break through the barrier field.
It's our only chance.
But how?
Just leave that part to me.
What's happening?
What have you done??
Shadow Angel...
Your luck... has changed!
Something that exists
in between my hands?
I don't know what he means...
There's nothing there.
Darkness?
There's nothing between
my hands but darkness...
Darkness and...
something else...
What is it?
There's warmth.
A light born out of darkness!
Silvia?
Brother.
Always remember...
you really are my other half.
Always.
Get away from me you filth.
What?
I can never forgive you
for what you've done.
I can't forgive you, but...
What is this.
Apollo, do you remember...
The day the world began,
there was nothing;
and there was everything...
There were billions of stars
swirling around in a great void,
light inside of darkness...
We were a part of it...
I think our souls knew
each other even then.
Our souls?
The part of us that
never changes...
no matter who we become...
or how many lives we live.
Since the world began...
I've loved you!
Silvia.
And now, together, we have to
mend the things we've broken.
I don't have to
do everything alone.
It's okay to need help.
I've felt so much pain,
so much hatred...
Is that what Toma was feeling
when Apollonius betrayed
him for Seliane... for me?
They have feelings
without wings.
They know pain... and joy.
I never understood how
the angels could suffer...
Watching their kind fade.
We thought only of ourselves.
And let the Earth die.
There's time... We can heal her.
Genesis merge!
They're actually Merging?
What the hell are they doing?
Look at the constellations...
They've become one!
Merge Form Genesis!
Go!
Aquarion!
It's never been like this.
It's... complete.
It feels like... I'm...
Free!
The Merge to Solar
Aquarion is complete.
I've never seen aura
levels this strong before!
Look...! They've really
done it... They've Merged.
They've done it.
They've become Solar Wing!
Apollo!
Thank you Silvia,
for everything.
I'll always remember this scent.
I'll never forget you.
Apo-
Don't leave.
I have to.
But I'll find you
again... I promise.
Apollo!
All right, it's time?
For the angels...
and the humans.
Prepare for... Genesis!
Chibiko!
She's waking up!
Hello, Chibiko.
Silvia?
How do you know me?
I saw Apollo in a dream...
He told me you
were going to find me.
A dream?
But where is he now?
Apollo... Where is he?
He had to leave... but don't
worry, he'll be back someday.
And until then...
You can see him there.