12,000 years ago in Atlantia,
brave warrior Angels
vigorously waged war,
pitting their skill and
technique against one another
at the valiant
Festival of Combat.
Now,... because of
Solar Wing's betrayal,
the Angels are gone
and our festival lights
have all but faded
away and disappeared.
It would not be wise
for us to allow Toma
to face Solar Wing on his own.
Moroha, a soldier
as powerful as you
deserves a creation
worthy of your skill...
A creation worthy of hosting
such an unparalleled
warrior and tactician.
Lensi, the architect said to
possess the fingers of God.
Tell me, my friend, what
have you created for me?
An unparalleled Cherubim
soldier, a flawless specimen.
So... two outta three?
But that was three.
Oh well, it's not like
anyone else can beat you
with a sword either.
Wanna bet?!
So it's you.
Moron, if he really
thinks he can beat
my brother he's
dumber than I thought.
No one can...
He's untouchable...
According to my calculations,
Apollo will last 4.8 seconds.
Sirius!
I was wrong!
Apollo can really fight!
Apollo is strong.
He definitely has raw talent,
but Sirius has
perfect technique.
It's nearly flawless.
Technique beats
strength every time.
Don't be so sure...
If you seek perfection
and gaze only toward
the stars in the sky...
...you will fail to see the
flowers on the ground...
What flowers?
He bit him!
No!
That's not fair.
You broke the rules.
When you're in a real fight,
your stupid "rules"
don't mean anything!
Get him!
Cherubim Soldier
detected in Yuze City!
Aquarion! Make ready for launch!
Pierre, Silvia, Apollo,
report immediately!!
Yeah!
I'm with him again?
I only want to
merge with you brother!
I know that Apollo
frustrates you,
but your feelings do not
negate the task at hand.
Fine... but I don't
have to like it!
All non-flight personnel
clear the decks immediately.
Vector docking
sequence complete!
Host Elements engaged!
Initiating Vector start up!
Power levels confirmed...!
Launch tracks activated...!
Launch gate is clear!
Ready for launch!
We can't find the
Cherubim in our database!
Merge as Aquarion
Luna for surveillance
but keep a safe distance!
Roger!
Forget it, I'm taking the lead!
What did you say?
You're just gonna screw it up!
I hate merging with you!
You're horrible at it!
You don't deserve
to be the head!
I'M horrible?!
This is no time
for petty arguing!
But... he started it!
You know the strongest
one should be the head!
Your ego's too
big to be the head!
It's about the right person for
the right situation... got it?
Screw that.
What a giant load of crap!
Follow your orders!
Still mad 'cause I beat you.
What?!
Guys we're about to merge!
What do you think you're doing?!
I told you, I'm the head!
Listen, we're here to fight a
Cherubim, not each other!
Hey old man.
You know what's up, right?
Tell 'em I'm the strongest!
That's enough!
Let's merge...
we need to do it now!
Roger that!
This isn't over yet Apollo!
Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go! Aquarion!!!
Let's do it!
They're sustaining damage!
Feedback levels rising!
Silvia!
I'm fine Brother!
Permission to relieve Silvia,
Commander Fudo!
No!
I can do it... I know I can!
That thing packs a mean punch.
We have to get outta here...
Retreat Apollo!
No way!
That... That Cherubim soldier...
Its aura...!
No... this high level
quantum pattern, it's...!
We're in trouble...
It looks like there's
a Shadow Angel on board!
Wingless fools!
Silvia!
Come on... get up!
Dodge!
Damn it!
I won't let a Shadow Angel win!
Silvia!
Apollo...
Her life aura is
dropping to critical!
Let me switch with her!
Oh no!!!
It's gone.
There's no response
from the vectors!
We need to get them outta there!
It's not over yet.
Please forgive me Moroha,
I have failed you.
With all my talent, not
even my most earnest effort
could create a soldier who could
withstand your absolute power.
Regardless, we managed
to immobilize them...
Solar wing is weaker
than I anticipated...
If we've witnessed the
full capacity of his power,
it would be
meaningless to acquire it.
What do you suppose
Toma will have to say?
I know what he'll say,
even if Solar Wing's power
has indeed fallen so low,
we still must not allow the
wingless one to possess it...
He'll demand victory.
Attention: until enemy activity
or receipt of further
instructions all elements
are ordered to stand by and
maintain your current position.
Her injuries are severe.
She needs a blood transfusion...
Or else... she may not make it.
We're the same blood type,
you can use mine.
Hey doc... use mine too.
Here... the more the merrier.
Get back...
This has nothing to do with you.
Hell it doesn't
Maybe if you knew
how to follow orders,
this never would've happened.
Yeah, but--
You animal, you're
not welcome here!
You jerk!
Come on...
Sirius is a better match...
They're brother and sister.
Don't worry about
Silvia, she'll be fine.
What I would worry
about is... we lost.
We've done all we can,
so now it's up to her...
Rest...
We're Alisians.
We're stronger than you think.
We'll be here if you need us.
Thanks.
We're strong.
Idiot...
Sirius...
Look...
Baron taught me about these...
They're really good for ya.
Tell your sister to eat it.
What the hell was that for?!
Am I unworthy?
I can't live with that.
Apollo.
They're serious.
You should be in bed!
Is brother okay?
He's not the same...
He's changed.
Do something Pierre...
Can you stop them?
I can't...
Why not...?
I know my brother wouldn't have
started something like this.
That beast Apollo
started it, didn't he?
I'm not so sure.
No!
Okay, that's
crossing the line...
I can't believe it.
Idiot... to lose my temper
over something like this!
Is that all you got?
You want more?!
You're a filthy beast!
It takes one to know one!
It's the the alarm!
How are the repairs coming?
We're not completely
finished yet sir!
Just as long as it flies...
That smell...
It's the one from yesterday!
Sirius!
Figures.
Let's go... I'll finish this.
Aquarion Luna!
Repair index is insufficient...
Luna won't survive.
What the--?!
Here it comes... Watch out!
We can't take much more of this!
I won't lose!
Hey!
This thing will pay for all the
Alisian blood it's spilled...!
I will avenge my sister!
Apollo!
What am I saying...?
Sirius!
Listen!
Leave me be!
Look down, by your feet!
Shut up!
You don't know
what you're doing!
Silvia!
My sister...
I- I almost...!
Luna element psyche
level is dropping.
Merge index falling!
They're breaking up...
We need to merge again!
Let me take lead this time!
I'm fine!
You didn't even know
Silvia was down there!
Keep her name out of
your mouth you beast!
Both of you need to get
your heads on straight...
We're here to avenge Silvia!
That's right... and I was the
one who failed to see her.
You see the sky but you
can't see the ground...
You're missing so much...
You must see
everything... Aquarion!
The world, I can see it!
I can see everything!
Too little too late...
it is done!
You can do better than that!
I didn't ask for your opinion!
I admit, I wasn't
seeing clearly,
but neither are you.
What the hell are you sayin'?!
You need me!
Shut up!
Come on!
Infinity Cross!!!
So that's Solar Wing...
This has suddenly
become more interesting...
They did it...
They won... together...
Oh brother...
will you forgive me?
What are you doing here?
I came to see Silvia.
She's asleep.
Come back tomorrow.
Misfortune is my symbol.
Bad luck is my identity.
Solitude and tragedy become me.
That is who I am.
Next on Aquarion: "Happiness is
at the Bottom of the Lake"