Its composition is
80 percent carbon,
10 percent hydrogen,
and 10 percent organic
compounds containing oxygen.
In other words: amber
The evidence suggests that the
feather was not placed inside...
But, it appears that the amber
formed around the
feather at its center...
So you're suggesting
the feather belonged
to some sort of winged dinosaur?
No, the dates
are too far apart...
We've used carbon dating to
establish a basic timeline...
Our data shows
it's 12,000 years old.
12,000 years old...?!
Impossible, amber is
fossilized tree resin...
There's no way it could've
formed in that span of time...
You've obviously
made a miscalculation!
A single feather sealed
in amber changes
the course of our journey...
It must be delivered
to Solar Wing...
This feather will bring about an
ultimate end to our bloody war.
Chapter 6, verse 7,
"The Mystery Song"
from the pages of the
Book of Holy Genesis.
If that's true, then...
...that would make this the most
important discovery of our time!
Says the man who was
sure we miscalculated!
Well naturally I'm a
bit skeptical, but...
when it comes to
the Shadow Angels,
we have to analyze
every possibility.
We must listen to the
words of Holy Genesis...
Treat them with the
respect they deserve.
Y'know, there are better
ways to spend a day off...
Are you just gonna
sit there all afternoon?
Yep.
Well, I tried...
I really hope I get
promoted this time...
Yeah? How'd your finals go?
Not good.
Hey... they're doing
"Giselle" at the ballet,
you wanna go with me?
"Giselle" is the
story of a poor woman
who gets taken advantage of by a
complete egotistical jerk.
You sure know
how to kill the mood?
Look, just don't walk so close.
Aw, come on Reika,
don't be like that!
I tried to warn you, Pierre--my
bad luck is contagious.
So does this mean you won't go
to the ballet with me...
Cause I really like you...
Bad luck or not!
Now... Your birthday
is coming up soon...
What should I get for you?
My birthday...?
That's not for weeks...
This thing looks interesting!
What is it?
Those were quite fashionable
in the 18th century.
It's a flea trap--women used to
wear them under their skirts...
What about this?
Silvia.
Oh... sorry...
Stop it right now Apollo!
Leave my brother alone!
He's the one who says he never
lets his guard down
He's an idiot, don't stoop to
the level of a child like him!
You're right this
is child's play.
I'm not a child...
I'm more of a man than you are.
You see?
The Barrier Field Generator...
Just look at it...
It's the top of the line.
The system isn't that different
from what you'd find
in any other city,
but its energy
output is way superior.
Cool stuff, huh?
The Barrier Field energy levels
depend on the geological strata.
The field is especially
strong here...
That's why DEAVA
chose to use this location.
How do you know all that?
I know everything!
What in the heck?
Those wingless bastards...!
They've broken the seal!
Are you saying
our feather has fallen
into the hands of
the wingless ones?
Yes, that is correct...
Lord Johannes!
What hopes were
invested in that feather?
The records are lost.
There is no question that the
feather came from Atlandia.
Therefore, we must assume
that the item contains
priceless information.
Lord Johannes,
we must get it back.
We can't afford to be hasty.
This could be a plan
by the wingless ones
to bait us into action.
Toma, you can't
seriously be considering
barging into Solar Wing's
lair by yourself?
And what would you
have me do, Moroha?
Sit back and allow
the filthy wingless ones
to discover the
secrets of our holy relic.
You misunderstand
Moroha's meaning...
No one is suggesting
we allow the wingless ones
to defile what
rightfully belongs to us.
The feather is being
held at the DEAVA base.
How will you be able
to break through the
Barrier Field Generator?
Leave that part
to me my friends.
Do you hear it...?
That strange sound?
The tree of life...
Do you remember the tree...?
There from the very beginning...
At the Genesis of the world.
Rena!
Someone call for a doctor!
Right!
Commander!
Well don't touch it,
we don't know what it might do!
Perhaps not...
Announce this to everyone...
Anyone who touches the
feather is going to be punished!
Why is that sir?
Don't ask questions...!
Answer them!
Brother.
Brother, what's wrong with you?
Go away!
Stay away from me!
Please stay away...
Please don't come near me.
Stay away from me!
Sirius!
Panties too tight.
Okay, that's not like you.
Silvia I know would punch me,
then kick me in the
teeth for good measure
Apollo!
Idiot!
See now there's
the Silvia I know!
Now... how 'bout we
go see the feather?
Fudo said not to touch it,
but you know me;
I've never been one
for following rules.
It might be able to tell
us something about Baron.
Baron, Baron...
It's always Baron with you!
Baron was my best friend...
Hell; my only friend.
They say that a fruit
never tastes as sweet
as the moment before it rots.
Master Toma...
We are prepared
to launch our attack...
You must wish to meet him
again... your dear friend.
I am going to meet someone
precious to me as well.
Very precious indeed.
Sophia...
Have you ever
told another person
that you were in love them?
Have you?
Yes.
Oh I see...
I'm so sorry.
Please don't...
It seems my question
has upset you...?
For all of my wisdom...
The mind of a woman is still
a complete mystery to me...
It's just a little mouse...
We'll let it go.
Hold up!
I smell something here.
Are you trying to tell me
you can actually smell
the infrared ions?
Ions...?
What the hell's an ion...?
All I know is it stinks!
I know this scent
from somewhere.
Where?
That's what I'm
trying to remember.
Apollo...! What's wrong?!
It's... It's the wing sign...
I remember it all so well
I screamed and
cried out for you...
And you... I heard you...
You heard me call
your name that day.
Apollonius.
Seliane.
If only... If only the
two of us had never met.
If only our stars
had never crossed...
For if we had never met...
I could have remained
a shadow angel...
The misfortune of our union.
And the joy...
The bliss of our meeting.
Seliane!
Apollonius!
I fell madly in love with you...
I fell in love
with a wingless one.
with you as well...
I fell madly in love with
a powerful Shadow Angel.
Apollonius.
I've been ordered to...
to execute you.
Then do it... Kill me.
Why?
Why...?!
Apollonius, I've captured
a foolish wingless creature
who was attempting
to save your life!
Seliane!
Apollonius!
How does it feel...?
To be so close, and
yet so utterly powerless
to save the life
of the one you love?!
No!
I will let the
wingless one go free...
I'll spare her life...
if you'll return to me.
Please.
Moroha...
Leave her with me...
I will take care
of this wingless fool.
I won't beg for my
life to a Shadow Angel!
Then you have chosen
the path of death!
No!
Apollonius!
You love her that much?
That much?!!!
We fought them...
We battled the Shadow Angels.
Together...
We fought to the end.
Seliane...
Apollonius...
What's the big idea?!
That's nasty!
Hey! You're the one who's nasty!
Do you remember what happened?
Uh... just barely.
In our previous lives we were...
Red Alert!
Attention Elements!
All personnel report
to command center.
DEAVA is under attack!
Hello, Solar Wing!
I've come for you.
Silvia! Pierre!
Fire... fist!
From 12,000 years of
suffering come quiet signs
of devastation and destruction.
Next time on Aquarion: "The
12,000-Year-Old Love Letter"!
It's... sort of nice.