Baron, no...
Baron!
Apollo, look out for
the little ones for me!
Baron!
Baron... Why was
I dreaming about him?
Are you alright, Silvia...?
It's late for you to be up.
I'm sorry to
bother you, Sophia...
I can't sleep...
I had a really strange dream.
Tell me about it.
Um, well... You see...
In my dream I saw
everything like I was Apollo.
That's interesting...
You're sure it was Apollo?
I think...
...I was walking in a forest...
and I was all alone.
Everything was dark.
And it was cold...
And then it began to snow.
Here!
Go ahead. Eat up...
I know it's not much,
but we gotta eat what we
can to survive, you know.
Are you kidding me...
How is he not freezing.
It's like he's from the sun...
Hey, I finally decided
on a name for ya!
A name?
Well as of today kid,
your name is Apollo...
Just like the mythological
god of the sun!
A- a... po... lo.
Apollo. Apollo!
I see...
So in the dream,
Baron was there...
And he gave you the name Apollo?
Ya, And then I was
sitting there with everyone...
Baron and all the others...
...and I knew their
names somehow...
I knew them.
And we were all
sharing food, like a family.
I don't know how
to explain it...
It felt like... home.
You felt very close to
these people, didn't you?
Ya... But then suddenly,
from nowhere, he was there.
It was that monster, Toma.
Forgive me... Master Johannes.
I regret that I was
unable to retrieve
the feather sealed in amber.
Are you telling me you
weren't able to learn
what information
the feather contained?
I'm sorry to say it,
but I learned nothing...
You aren't quite living
up to your name.
What is it they call you...
"Exalted Angel"...?
Your affection for that traitor
has made you weak, Toma...
No doubt that is why you
failed to retrieve the feather.
No...! Master Toma
would never hold on
to such foolish feelings.
Then why exactly has
he adorned a helmet
with the feathers of that
cursed traitor Apollonius...
And why is it that he carries
it with him wherever he goes?
Twelve thousand years ago,
Apollonius was chosen
for the sacred act
that would ensure
the continuation of our kind...
But he betrayed us,
me most of all.
I carry the helmet
as a reminder of this
and of my own foolishness.
Well... It sounds
to me a bit like
you haven't quite let
go of those old feelings.
We'll leave it
at that, Moroha...
More importantly, we need to
know if Solar Wing's powers
are developing to the strength
of his previous incarnation.
Master, from what
I have observed,
his powers are still
far from what they were
when he fell from our grace
twelve thousand years ago...
Though he has not yet
come fully back to himself,
he has begun exhibiting powers
that even we do not possess...
It is imperative that Solar Wing
regain sufficient power
to pollinate the Tree of Life...
If he is unable to
join with the Tree
and create the fruit that
will bring forth a new world,
then we have no
further use for him.
There are some things which
are beyond our control...
If Solar Wing
proves useless to us
then I will see to his
destruction personally.
After Toma appeared in my dream,
time began to
jump around, like...
like I was reliving my life and
someone else's at the same time.
It was twelve thousand years ago
when my beloved
Apollonius left me...
He wasn't the only one
I remembered losing.
When I was young...
my mother left.
And then my father. And now...
And now Baron's gone too
because they took him from me.
Silvia, these feelings
aren't yours alone...
They're his too... Apollo's.
How is that possible?
He's dealing with the loss
of someone incredibly
important to him...
And it's tearing him up.
Ya I know.
I think his sadness was so great
that it somehow invaded your
heart and entered your dreams...
So what you're feeling right
now are not just your emotions,
but Apollo's as well.
You're saying Apollo's
feelings are inside me?
That's so gross...!
You can't be serious.
Wings huh?
He remembers...
Something from his past life.
Apollo has memories
of being Solar Wing.
Look, that's not what I said?
You didn't have to.
He touched the feather that was
embedded in amber, didn't he...?
When you two snuck into
the laboratory that day.
Yes...
He touched it... and then we...
started seeing things...
We shared visions
of their past...
We saw their memories...
Apollonius... and Seliane.
I see...
Silvia, I'm sure you're telling
the truth about all this,
but I'm afraid we can't
just assume that what you
and Apollo saw were really
memories of past lives...
There are too many
other explanations.
But?
I'm sorry to tell you...
A memory's a strange thing...
And it isn't always
that accurate.
It's possible that your minds
have created false memories,
drawing them from
everything you've heard about
the Book of Holy Genesis
since you came to DEAVA.
I've never heard
of false memories.
Remember, too, that the
feathers of the Shadow Angels
contain many powers
that we don't understand...
It's possible that information
from twelve thousand years ago
was recorded in
that feather somehow...
Perhaps the two of
you managed to access
and read that information,
and then you internalized it.
And there's one more thing
you need to consider, Silvia...
It's possible that,
while you were in the
presence of the feather,
some of your
unconscious memories
were transferred to Apollo...
He could have seen
them... felt them...
...and easily mistaken them
for memories of his own.
What...?
Y- you think Apollo could
have seen my memories...?
No way, that's not possible!
Is it really that unlikely...?
You did just see
Apollo's memories
in your dream, didn't you?
Well, yeah...
but that's different.
Here's what I think.
When you Merge
to become Aquarion,
you cease to be
three individual people...
The minds and hearts of
each Element start to overlap.
As a result of this,
I think you're beginning
to share each other's
feelings and memories.
Share feelings with him?!
With my brother, maybe...
But never with that beast...!
I don't want him wondering
around inside my head!
Oh really... Then why
did the two of you
merge together so well
if you detest him so much?
It feels... so good!
I...
Well, the heart can certainly
be a troublesome thing...
You'd think it would be easy,
but sometimes the hardest part
is figuring out
how you really feel.
How do I do that...?
Figure it out?
How horrible.
This doesn't look good.
Incoming!
Where is it?!
Something's wrong...
I can't find the target.
Why can't we see it?
I think the enemy
is using an invisibility
shield to hide itself.
So that's their game!
We won't accomplish
anything like this.
We have to Merge
and look for it!
Right!
Aquarion Luna!
I have to stay calm...
That's the only
way I'll find it.
It's there!
Stay calm!
We've got it!
What the...?!
It was a decoy.
That's enough... We're
running out of options, Jun Lee!
Become the head and use psychic
imaging to find the target!
Me as the head?
You've got to be joking!
That's just reckless!
Come on, Jun.
It's time to act like a man!
Yeah... sure.
Go Merge One.
Merge Two!
G- Go... Aquarion!
This is incredible!
Aquarion... Mars!
Alright!
Jun...
Stop fooling around,
Aquarion, and find the target!
Roger that.
Searching for an image.
It's close!
You were too slow, Jun...!
You have to act faster!
I have to find it...
Have to find... ...the image.
Jun, no!
He's gotta do better than that.
He's pitiful.
That kid wasn't ready
to be the Head Element.
Enough...!
Silence yourselves and try
to see what you're looking at.
Huh?
See what?
You look at him and see nothing
but a fool tripping
all over himself.
Have to find... the image.
But when I look at him, I see
a kid who's scared to death,
who's doing everything he can
to fight an enemy
that he can't see...
And he's doing all this
while coping with the terror
of being the Head Element
for the first time and the fear
of disappointing the people
who are depending on him.
Cant' you see how
hard he's trying for you?!
Commander.
Come on...
you have to find it now.
Seliane!
Apollonius, I hear you.
Jun...! Reika...! Pierre...!
Respond...
please somebody respond!
Element bioenergy
is fading rapidly...
They're approaching
critical levels...!
Why are you
just sitting there...?
We gonna give these
guys a real fight, or what?
I think he's awakened.
We're fighting for lost lives!
Seliane! Come!
What?
What the...
Did you really just say Seliane?
He's delusional... that's all...
Has this beast of a boy
remembered a past life?
All right everyone... Let's go!
Everybody?!
All Elements are instructed
to standby for teleport change!
Genesis Form...
Go! Aquarion!
It's never been
like this before.
They killed Baron, Seliane!
Their time is up... Now!
He mentioned Baron and
Seliane in the same breath...
Apollo's confusing his
past life with the present.
Stay calm, everyone.
We'll only find the enemy if
we quiet our minds and focus.
This from you?
Which one of them is
the real Solar Wing?
I don't know anymore.
Luna Element's emotional
aura is developing a split wave!
I'm reading great confusion!
Silvia, hold on.
This is serious, Seliane.
You have to quiet
your mind, and quickly.
You can shut up now...!
You think you can
order me around?
If you were really the
reincarnation of my dead lover,
you'd be nicer to me.
So who are you...?
Tell me now!
You know who I am.
What's happening to Aquarion?
Vector Sol has disappeared!
Where's Apollo? He's Gone!
He's disappeared?
He's disappeared... He's gone.
What's going on?
Where are you, Apollo?
Using the Mystic Veil was an
excellent idea, Master Toma...
We can see if Solar Wing
enjoys being invisible...
I wonder what those fools will
do when they think he's gone.
One of the greatest faults
of the wingless ones
is that they trust only what
they can see...
This should be interesting,
watching them fall
pathetically apart.
Where are you?
Answer me... Damn it!
Is it possible...?
Could he be dead?
He's there...
If anything had
happened to Apollo,
the whole Merge would have
fallen apart right away.
I can sense an unseen force...
And with it, an unseen heart.
Apollo...! This is not cute!
Apollo.
Baron!
No...! Baron...! No!
What...?
Calm down now, Silvia!
Come on now,
this is no time to panic!
Just get away, Brother...!
You don't know what I'm feeling!
What?
What's... happening?
Silvia.
Forgive me... I don't...
I'm sorry!
Silvia... Sister.
What's happening to me?
You think it would be easy,
Silvia, but sometimes
the hardest part is figuring
out how you really feel.
No!
How did this happen...?
It's Apollo...
It was always Apollo...
and now he's gone.
What's going on...?
It looks like some kind of
storm's surrounding Silvia.
Silvia's pulse and blood
pressure are rising too rapidly!
If it continues like this,
she could be in danger!
I see it now...
Why couldn't I before?
Where are you?
So she finally figured it out.
Let's take care of this, Silvia.
You got it.
It's been there, hiding
in the shadows all along.
The trick... is knowing
where to look.
Apollo... This is for you.
Thank you... Silvia.
As far as I'm concerned,
the people who talk about
how sweet love is don't
know how bitter it can be...
It's better to Merge...
That way, if anyone hurts you,
you can just give
them a Fire Kick!
Next on Aquarion:
"Aquarion's First Love."