What the hell does that mean?
It means "person"...
Can't you see it...?
It's actually a form of two
people supporting each other.
That's stupid, it's two lines.
Look close...
It's not stupid, it's beautiful.
Hey there, Tsugumi.
Hey, Pierre, what's up?
Busy Saturday?
I've got tickets to El Sueno...
You wanna go with me?
Do you really want me to go?
Sophia, hey!
Well that's an ambitious switch.
What a jerk.
Hey, so I was thinking
you and I could go see-
What's this...?
Well, it's a
letter for Pierre...
I guess one of your girlfriends
doesn't have internet access.
We've been lucky so far.
The Harvest Beasts haven't
appeared here in San Jose.
Hopefully they never will...
So don't worry.
Our entire family is fine... Be
safe, Pierre.
Don't go playing the hero and do
something reckless, okay?
P.S... Our brother Lopez is
getting married next month...
You'll never guess who to...
Esperanza...
What, is that all you got...?
Now, let's shoot to score!
White hot...
...fire kick!
That was way too easy...
You girls up for round two?
C'mon, there's gotta be
another Harvest Beast
around here somewhere!
What's gotten into him?
I don't know.
You okay...?
What happened to all
that energy you had earlier?
Guess I used it all up...
Controlling myself around
you pretty girls. That's all.
I recognize bad luck
when I see it, Pierre.
No, I'm fine.
What...?! Who did that...?
A- Apollo!
What's your problem,
man, what's the big idea?
Figured it would
liven you up some.
Is that how you liven up
people who look depressed?
By hitting them?!
Well... it worked didn't it.
What's wrong with you?
Whatever, I've got
better things to do.
I need to do it.
Don't care with who...
So, as you can see...
Aquarion's Merge Index is
defined by the Element's aura,
which we call Alpha...
This aura determines the level
of quantum patterns necessary
to create a bond
between the Elements.
But this is also determined
by planetary alignment...
We call this aspect Beta.
These factors have
the strongest effect...
But there's also the
influence of sunspots.
And of course...
there's the allure of the
Earth's magnetic field which
pulls these factors together.
These elements characterize
the given amount of energy...
I wanna do it.
Excuse me, Pierre!
Please explain merge in your
own words for the class; and go!
Yes...!
Let's do it!
Um... I appreciate your
enthusiasm, but "Let's do it"
is not an accurate explanation
of the merge equation.
How cute!
Pierre, you and Esperanza
look great together!
You are so disgusting!
I didn't wear this skirt
so you could stare up it!
I hope that hurts...
That's what you get
for looking... Pervert.
Whoa, don't you
have anything to say?
Pierre's not
really himself today.
What's weird is he
wasn't looking at her.
Part of him is missing.
He's dead inside.
Mi- missing?
What do you mean "dead inside"?
Bravo...!
Bravissimo, Pierre!
Pierre!
What's wrong with you...?!
Snap out of it!
I need it...
I need to merge...
I need... I need...
Apollo...! Hold him down!
I need to merge!
It seems that Pierre has
become addicted to merging.
Pierre's addicted...?
What's that supposed to mean?
Addiction is a sickness
where you can't live
without something.
I get that, but we're
talking about Pierre?
I'm afraid that he is...
His dopamine levels
have dramatically dropped
since his last merge...
This clearly shows dependency.
But he's going to
be all right, isn't he?
This was just a simulation...
You saw his reaction...
If this... If this had
been a real merge, then...
...his mental state would
have probably collapsed.
A Harvest Beast has been
detected over San Jose...!
All Elements...
Prepare to launch!
San Jose... No, it can't be!
Let me out...!
Let me out of here!
Esperanza!
Lopez...! Get out of here!
I'm not leaving.
Alright, let's do this!
Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go, Aquarion!
Ah... The Wingless
Ones have arrived.
Lets do some damage!
Apollo...! There's
another one behind us!
What the?!
Lets even the odds!
Easy enough...
Why do they bother?
Apollo, look!
Focus...
Psychic eye!
Analyzing internal structure!
There it is...!
The other one is
the controlling unit!
That's not fair!
But now that we know that...
his cheating ass is ours!
Infinity Punch!
That got him!
How the...?
Jun...! Wasn't
that the controller?!
Whoa...
The weak spot's
moving between them!
What do you mean "moving"?!
No way!
Kumbha and Nikumbha.
Two bodies sharing
a single heart.
If Kumbha is in battle, the
heart moves to Nikumbha...
In effect, their heart is
never exposed to danger.
Together they are invincible...
They'll never stop...
They'll fight for
the span of eternity,
if that's what it takes.
But... How long can
the Wingless Ones last?
Vector Luna...!
Do you copy...?
Vector Luna!
Silvia's bio-energy
levels are dropping!
Her aura is weakening!
I'm not sure how much
more she can take!
Silvia.
Initiate Teleport...!
Tsugumi, switch with Silvia!
Sir!
Apollo... Jun...
We can do this.
Chloe! Man her station...!
We've got a long
battle ahead of us.
Stay alert, everyone!
I could strangle
Pierre right now...
What a perfect
time to be useless.
Merge One!
Merge Two!
Let me do it!
Pathetic!
Chloe, take Jun's place!.
Reika, take over for Tsugumi.
Roger!
Let me out of here, now!
Let me... Let me merge!
Merge One!
Merge Two!
Go, Aquarion!
Aquarion Luna!
Spinning Blades!
Divine Wind Blade!
Dragon... Thunder!
We got him.
Look out!
This character...
means "person" yet it's two
people supporting each other.
Seems rather trite to me.
Two people relying on
one other for support?
They'll inevitably
become weak and fall.
I... I need...
You have to let me merge!
If you're going to support
another, then you better
be able to support yourself
without their help.
And if you're going to collapse,
you should fall alone.
Initiate Teleport...!
Sirius for Reika!
Yes, sir!
Please... She needs me...
Let's end this!
A direct hit.
Finally.
What?
Chloe!
Her bio-energy's dropping!
Teleport...!
Send the next available cadet!
There's no one else...
Get the trainees...!
It's an emergency!
Quit sniveling... You had
the best simulation scores
in your class, you'll be fine.
Sir!
San Jose... is my home!
You can't stop me!
You can't...!
You could be paralyzed!
Wait, come back!
You sure about this?
Merging might destroy me,
but if that's what it takes to
save my loved ones, so be it.
You mean it, don't you?
My family lives in San Jose.
Your family?
Well... why didn't you say so...
Merge One!
Go Merge Two!
Go, Aquarion!
What's wrong?
Feels like I'm burning.
What is this heat?
Aquarion... Mars!
Firekick!
We're not done yet!
Let's go for the goal!
Dribble, dribble,
dribble, dribble, dribble.
Dribble, dribble, dribble...
Dribble, dribble...
This is impossible...
Aquarion's
engulfed in flames...!
We're on fire!
Dribble and shoot!
Pierre! Pierre!
He's not responding!
Apollo! Try to slow us down!
Right!
Wake up! Esperanza! Come on!
You have to get up...!
Esperanza, please,
they're coming back...!
She'll be fine, Anna,
she's fine, I promise...
Lopez... Esperanza.
Goodbye... Pierre.
Pierre! His levels have
reached critical status!.
He's dying!
Chief!
Apollo! You have to
try to undo the merge!
Or try to find some
way to pilot Aquarion!
Forget it... This fight
belongs to Pierre, not me.
You're not serious!.
He can't fight,
he's on the verge of dying!
He has to do this!
It's his battle, I won't
take that away from him!
We saw the flames of his passion
and only he can put them out.
This is insubordination...
Fine, you leave me no choice!
I'll override the merge!
They're not disengaging...!
What's going on?!
The merge index
is too elevated...
Aquarion's not responding
to any remote commands.
But that's impossible!
Try to get up... Pierre!
He can't rise.
He hasn't finished collapsing...
So how could he possibly get up
if he's still in the
process of falling?
He must fall...
Let him fall the whole way.
Before a person
can support another...
He must be able to
stand and carry himself...
We stand alone
to stand together,
he still craves support.
Craves support?
You mean his
addiction to merging?
That's okay...
You're not the only woman.
I don't need to need you.
I was...
I was just hoping
someone would carry me,
because I was scared?
After a person has
entirely collapsed,
he is left with only
one possible choice.
He has to stand up
with both of his feet
firmly planted on the ground.
Just like this character.
A person must spread
his arms to be...
Great!
Rise up... on... your... own!
Esperanza!
Lopez, Anna!
Are you alright?
Here, hold on to me.
I can't believe it.
Ole...! Aquarion!
Pierre hey,
Come in!
I haven't kicked the bucket yet!
Then lets kick ass.
Aquarion is back up!
Are they okay?
All systems seem to be normal!
Energy levelssteadily rising!
Amazing!
Has Pierre
overcome the addiction?
These boys don't
know when to quit.
Go for the goal, Pierre.
Let's finish this
game and win it!
Damn straight.
Fire up!
Heartbreak... attack!
And Pierre approaches
for the final kick!
He shoots!
It looks good... And he scores!
Bravissimo!
So the fire is within them.
Yes, and I want it to burn...
Burn brightly...
for our grand resurrection.
Could it really be?
Good luck, you two.
Releasing... merge bond.
I'm happy Pierre's
fully recovered...
I was afraid that he wouldn't.
Me too.
But from this point on...
I'm going to carefully observe
all the Elements'
psychological conditions...
If one of you
could become addicted,
then it can happen again.
I highly doubt that.
You never know...
Although, thankfully,
no one else
seems quite as
susceptible as Pierre.
But I'll still run full checks
on all of you, just to be safe.
Yeah.
Mirror, mirror,
on the wall...
Tell me who's the
loveliest of them all.
Please, you have
to let me do it.
I want to merge,
I want to merge.
Rena, what are you?!
Next time on Aquarion:
"Black Mirror."
I need to merge!