It is year eleven
of the Holy Genesis...
The Earth, which
was laid to ruin
during the Great
Catastrophe, is now plagued
by relentless attacks from
the Shadow Angels of Atlandia,
who have awakened
after 12,000 years ...
The planet's only chance
for survival lies in the
hands of the Elements...
a group of extraordinary
youths whose rare gifts
have enabled them to set
forth on this noble mission.
They have been chosen to
unite in mind, body, and soul
in the hopes that
their combined power
will be the salvation
of the human race.
Aquarion!
Such incredible power...!
It feels... so good...!
Master...
The Wingless Ones...
Yes.
Otoha, how long
have I been at rest?
12,000 years my lord.
12,000 years...?
And what has become
of the Lower World?
The Earth is in
a state of decline,
as it has been ever since
that foolish human ate
of the Fruit of Knowledge...
It has become a vile place...
So... the Wingless Ones continue
to defile our grand
dreams of paradise...
My lord... you must know...
The one who betrayed us...
The one who betrayed you...
Solar Wing...
He's been resurrected...
hasn't he?
It would seem so...
And he seeks to
battle us once again...
Then we shall give
him what he wants.
I'll ask you one more time...
What's your name...?
How old are you...?
Do you have any family?
Look...
It's been a long day.
Why don't you make
it easier on all of us...
Just a couple answers
and we're through.
It's easy...
What's your name...?
How old are you...?
Do you have any family?
I am talking to you...!
You deaf?!
You filthy street rat?!
Hey...! Get Down!!
Stay right where you are!!
C- Commander...?
Who are you?
So you do speak...
Well, before I answer
your questions...
You'll do the polite thing...
and answer ours first.
Now for the last time...
What do you call yourself?
Apollo.
Apollo... a fine name.
So, brother?
We did it--our first Merge!
What was it like for you?
It was like the entire
world had been reborn.
It felt like ten thousand
white roses caressing me...
It was like waking up to
the face of my one true love.
Such incredible power...
...so good...!
Yeah... me too.
There was a blinding light...
It was beautiful... like
something from another world
like it was shining
down from paradise...
At least that's what I thought.
I'll never forget that
first merge with Reika.
You were talking about her?!
Maybe I saw the ultimate
light the light of creation
the Alisia family's spent
centuries searching for
to finally guide us to complete
peace and understanding...
But... I didn't see
it the second time.
Not with that boy...
I can't believe a man as
smart as Fudo is convinced
he's the reincarnation
of Solar Wing.
It's sacrilege.
The time I merged with Apollo
was so violent and aggressive...
Not beautiful, the way a
real merge is supposed to be.
It's true...!
That's why it can't be him!
He can't!!
He simply can't be
the Solar Wing...!
Everyone knows
that it's you, brother.
Silvia... You mustn't be so
frivolous with your claims.
But why?
It's dangerous.
Damn you!!!...!
Let me out of this hell hole!!
Look at him...!
Is this kid for real...?
I've seen rabid dogs more
well behaved than this urchin.
It stretches the imagination...
to think he's the same Solar
Wing who saved the human race
in the battle of Atlandia
12,000 years ago.
Who can say?
You... You mean to tell me that
you don't know for certain...?!
You allowed a complete novice,
you know nothing about...
...to pilot Aquarion
without being sure?!
Apollo was chosen by Aquarion.
In the same way a
horse chooses its rider...
Aquarion chose that boy.
Huh, well, if that's true,
it does seem an odd choice...
I'm starving.
Here!
Go ahead. Eat up...
I know, it's not much, but...
We gotta eat what we
can to survive, ya know?
Baron...
You don't have to
be so afraid of me...
I won't hurt you.
You really are an animal.
That's what Commander
Fudo says that there's a beast
of darkness trapped within
you, waiting to be freed...
And you believe him?
Well, I'm not sure I see
you the way he does...
You're... blind?
I have other ways of seeing...
I don't need to use my eyes.
I was curious so I
came to find out:
are you Solar Wing
or just an empty headed beast?
You don't even know do you?
Makes you wonder, huh...?
I mean, if our top three
Elements get the crap kicked out
of 'em in their
first real battle, well...
It's too bad they
didn't send me out there.
Things would'a turned out a lot
differently, I tell you that.
Oh please... Send you out...?
Don't be absurd.
Sure, you think
just 'cause you're
some kinda prince,
your better than me?
Well you got another
thing coming pal!
Reika?
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault...
If I hadn't lost it up there
none of this would've happened.
This town... and Glen.
Don't be so hard on yourself...
It's my fault too.
I should have done
more to support you...
Sirius, no.
Get away from him!
Silvia?
You bring nothing
but bad luck...
I don't want you
anywhere near my brother!
Anyone who gets involved
with you ends up hurt or dead!
But I...
Silvia!
It's true!
No... It's okay...
Your sister's right.
Stand by at launch pad!
This is not a drill,
I repeat, this is not a drill.
All pilots to launch pad.
Begin launch sequence!
Vector docking
sequence complete!
Host Elements engaged!
Initiating Vector start up!
Power levels confirmed!
Status check: all systems green!
Configurations complete...
Clear for take-off.
All Vectors standing by,
ready for launch!
Initiating countdown
sequence, ten seconds...!
9... 8... 7...
6... 5... 4... 3...
Vector Sol, ready for takeoff!
Vector Mars, taking off!
Vector Luna, taking off!
Harvest Beast sighted...
It's directly ahead!
So merciless.
I'm not gonna let you
down this time, Glen.
Vector Sol to team...
Formation S-L-M.
Code-name...! Battle Leviathan!
Quantum levels augmented.
Aura resonance at Merge level.
Merge One!
Go Merge Two!
Go...! Aquarion--
Do you sense something?
I don't know.
Baron...
Delicious.
There's something wrong
with Reika's psyche level!
The fear in Aquarion's
response field has spiked!
Help her...!
She's having some
kind of a flashback!
Syncro Failure!
Merge index has dropped
to critical levels...
Abort merge!
Vector Sol: Multi-dimensional
quantum levels fading rapidly!
Commander!
Let me trade places with her...!
We could do a teleport transfer!
Teleport transfer...?
Are you sure you want to
do something that dangerous?
If I didn't know better, I'd say
you were worried about me.
I'm worried about Reika,
not you, you big ape.
You're no fun, Chloe...
Seriane!
Why are you
just sitting there...?
I thought you were a fighter?!
What's wrong with you?
Have you forgotten
your warrior's pride?
Seriane!!
A- Apollonius...?
How dare you lecture me!
Who was that?!
He's calling Silvia
from her past life.
Then why don't you join with me
and prove you haven't
lost your will to fight!
This is amazing...
They've both crossed
into a past existence.
Move... I'm going in.
Have you completely lost it...?
I don't want to have
to hurt you again.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Start the transfer.
Will somebody get down
there and drag him off?!
Not so fast.
Now listen up... prepare for
immediate teleport transfer!
You heard him...
But commander, please...
You can't do this.
We don't know
anything about that kid.
And that's precisely why we
ought to test him and find out.
Activate the teleport sphere.
Teleport countdown...
5... 4... 3... 2... 1.
Transfer!!
Teleport complete.
Someone get a medic!
Let's go, you two!
We don't follow you!
This cretin actually
thinks he's Apollonius...?
Impossible!
Genesis Merge... Go!!!
How is he doing this...?!
Quantum levels augmented!
Merge index increasing!
Aquarion!!!
Let's take him out!!
The light...!
This could be the
light we've waited for
these last 12 millennia?
Master Toma...
Otoha... the transmission song.
The soul transmission
song... play it.
That voice...
Sounded like singing...
Wait--what voice?
It came back to life.
And it's even
stronger than before.
So that's how
we're gonna play it.
The Cherubim Soldier's
quantum levels
have increased seven times.
What?! Impossible.
You must've made a mistake.
It's no mistake!
Come on, somebody let me at it.
The body's too heavy...
Who's controlling the legs?
You're reaction
time is too slow!
Too slow?!
Here it comes!
What are you doing...?!
C'mon Seliane, you're supposed
to be guarding the rear!!
Oh yeah? Says who?!
This isn't a real merge!
We're not in sync at all!!
No!
Hurry...!
Do something Apollo!!
Come on!!
You've grown weak...
What's become
of you, Solar Wing?
Who's that?!
It's coming from the Cherubim!
Time has stripped
you of your glory...
There's not even a glimmer
of the strong, beautiful
Wing I once knew.
It's him...
It has to be... Toma!
Toma...
It's so... so cold.
What is this...?
This feeling--like
the light inside
my soul has suddenly
gone dark...
Their aura levels are down!
Their hearts are being
consumed by the darkness!
He's reached the edge.
Apollo's soul has fallen
into the inner depths
of his consciousness.
Solar Wing...
Please... Shine your light.
My light...?
The light which betrayed us
and cast a shadow
over this world...
The ultimate light.
Awaken, Solar Wing...
Take your rightful
place by my side.
My beloved.
It's too late!
Yes...! That's it!!
So the beast within
has spread its wings...
It's the light born
out of darkness...
The Genesis Light from which
the whole universe was made!
The purest light.
The light... I once loved.
What...?! I can't
do the preview!
Don't be silly,
of course you can, brother!
Everything you do is perfect!
Very well...
Next time on Aquarion:
"Element School."
There, you see...?
I knew you'd be great at it!