Reika.
How'd you know?
I could sense you...
And the sound of your footsteps
rings like music in my ears.
Look up there...
Those clouds look
like angel wings.
The clouds seem so lonely...
in the way they're
always wandering the sky...
never able to find
what they're searching for.
Sometimes I feel that way.
I've never thought of that...
The loneliness... and
the constant searching...
You really are a poet, Sirius.
Reika.
I'm sorry for using you...
Just so I could avoid
the traps in the labyrinth.
Fudo's always telling us
that we should use
all available resources...
You were just doing what
you needed to, that's all.
Thank you for being
so understanding Reika.
You can't...!
Your sister was right when
she told you I was bad luck.
I wish she would
leave him alone.
Hey, ice cream!
What's the matter with you?!
That ice cream was supposed
to be a special
surprise for my brother!
You see...
You'll only get hurt.
Okay class, today we'll
begin an exercise designed
to channel your thoughts
into long distance attacks...
Your partners will position
themselves at the foot
of those mushroom mountains,
and you will cause them
to turn around by using the
power of your own thoughts.
One question sir...
Are we permitted
to make them turn around
by using mental telepathy?
You miss the point.
This exercise isn't
simply putting words
into your partner's head...
it's about using
your mental energy...
to physically impose
your will on others.
And we're supposed to do
this with just our thoughts?
But it's so far.
What a waste of time...
At that distance...? No way.
It's gonna crash!
How did he do that?
We're about to find out...
Let's try this!
1... 2... 3...
How'd I get stuck with you?
I'm not happy about
this either, you know.
I... I can't seem to
get away from you.
I know... I guess its destiny.
Jun, you and Rena standby
to take aura measurements.
You seem nervous.
Haven't you ever
held a girl's hand?
No... I...
O-Of course I have!
Here goes nothing.
Psychokinesis!
It's not working!
She's too far.
Okay, strike...!
Come on, already...! Strike!!
He has an impressive aura...
Too bad he can't control it.
His aura levels
are off the chart.
Okay, but what good does
it do if he can't harness it?
Commander, their ESP is
still severely underdeveloped,
not to mention unstable...
Perhaps we should
start a shorter distance
in order boost their confidence.
Distance isn't the problem.
It only seems far to them
because they believe it's far...
Their hearts... are weak.
Distance and time
are simply constructs
of an uncertain spirit.
So we create them?
Interesting.
I sense the
Solar Wing has invaded
your thoughts once
more, Master Toma...
Actually, I was
thinking about you.
You tease me, my lord.
Master Toma, wait...!
The moon becomes
you tonight, my lord.
Like you it teases:
Close enough to bask
in the light of its beauty,
but too far away to
ever hope to touch it.
I suppose it's in my nature...
Never close, yet never far.
Yes... that's perfect.
I still don't feel anything.
Hey Tsugumi!
How about next time
you partner with me?
Give it a rest Pierre.
She's too young for you.
Okay... if old man Fudo
can do it, then so can I...
Just concentrate!
Come on!!!!
Use your voice one more
time and you're disqualified.
Shut your face!!
What an idiot.
Alright, it's time to give
it everything I've got...
Maximum Psychokinesis!!!
Well, I guess it kind of worked.
You screwed up big time!
Shut up!!
Apollonius...!
Apollonius, hang on!!
Seriane, Please, don't let go!!
Reach me...
You can do it... just try!
Apollonius, don't leave me!!!
This better be good.
I have a small favor to ask you.
I'm not interested in being
your trap fodder again, okay?
That isn't what
I want Reika, I promise...
I just thought that
you could help me
practice the technique
we learned today.
Okay... why ask me...?
Wouldn't your sister
be a better choice
for something like this?
Silvia's still a little girl...
She's so wrapped up
with her own feelings
that she can't be bothered to
concern herself with others.
I see...
The Book of Holy
Genesis makes it clear...
The Shadow Angels will
continue to grow in power
if they're allowed to keep
harvesting human prana...
It's up to us to stop them,
but we're not going to be able
to unless we get stronger too.
I'll do it for the sake of Glen
and everybody else that
they've taken, but that's it...
It isn't because of you.
It's so beautiful.
A night-blooming cereus,
a blossom that only
thrives in the darkness.
It suits you.
Well if you say so.
The way things have
been going lately,
I'm never gonna find
a way to rescue Baron.
Why do I keep smelling flowers?
They're practicing...?
Not without me they're not.
Well if my Sword of
the Heart can't reach her.
I'm sorry I couldn't save
you 12,000 years ago...
But I won't make the same
mistake in this life...
This time I'll make sure my
feelings reach my true love...
After all, brother...
you are the true Solar Wing.
Maybe I should get closer.
Come on brother!
It should work from here.
The Heart's Arrow...!
It worked!!
Sirius!!
Did it reach you?!
Why did it hit Apollo?!
Silvia!!
Oh don't mind me...
I was just practicing...
Silvia!...!
How did I know it was you?!!
Sirius!!
Reika?!
Careful!
Unit Two requesting
reinforcements!!
Let's get this over with
before it can do any
more damage to the city...
Use the Trinity Saber formation.
Roger!
What are you
doing up there?!...!
Filing your nails?!
Be quiet...
I need to concentrate.
Long Range Saber Strike!!
What the?!!
What happened?!
It's figured out Aquarion
Mars' attack range.
Hey Sirius...!
You should attack
with the Heart's Arrow...!
All you have to do is
concentrate like before...
Like when you aimed at my heart!
At your what?!!
What are you talking about?!
Excellent idea...
Good work Reika.
Silvia...
We're going to switch
to Aquarion Luna.
You handle the bow,
and I'll take care of the arrow.
Fine.
If you say so...
but its only because
you're my big brother.
Hey Princess Screw Up...
I hope you can drive
better than you can throw.
I'll show you!
If Reika can manage to pilot
this thing then so can I!
Knock it off,
you two... Merge One!
If you say so... Merge Two!
Go...! Aquarion!!
It feels so good!
Aquarion... Luna!!
Oh wow...!
So this is what it feels
like to be the head...!
Silvia...! Its time to focus!
Right... Lunatique... Archery!!!
Long Range... Arrow!!!
Okay, I'm ready!!
Her aim is terrible... Don't
forget that.
Not to worry... I'll do the
targeting.
Okay!!
Now!!
Keep going...
Keep going... Keep going!
Where did it go?!
So what are we
supposed to do now?!
You continue to
amaze me, Master...
What an ingenious idea,
imbuing the Cherubim Soldier
with the moon's
ability to appear close,
yet remain untouchable.
Tell me...
What will you do now...?
Solar Wing.
Switch over to Solar Aquarion!!!
Geez... It took you long enough!
But Commander, he failed
the training exercises...
It isn't fair.
That's enough, Sirius...
You've made it clear to me
that your heart isn't ready
to do what I've asked of you.
What's that supposed to mean?
Alright... Let's get started!
Incredible!
This is gonna to be tricky...
I'm stuck with a couple
of talent-less royal
pains in the neck...
It's not a lot to work with...
But if we can combine
all of our powers...
We just might have a chance.
Apollo, I've
spotted the soldier!
Alright buddy,
time for you to go...
Silvia... Sirius...
I'm going to need
your help, okay?
Did he just ask for our help?
I suppose he did...
Let's do it Silvia.
Yeah... Okay!
Ready, NOW!!!!
Not so fast!!
No way!
Yeah! Bull's eye!
But why...?!
I thought for sure
it would work!
He's using his thoughts...
When he should
be using his heart.
You cannot expect to move
mountains with thought alone.
I don't understand
what happened!
Why didn't our punch
have any effect?!!
Come on Sirius...
Think.
Their hearts... are weak...
Distance and time
are simply constructs
of an uncertain spirit.
Apollo...!
You've got to stop putting
limits on your power!!
What did you say?!
Stop trying to
hit the Soldier...!
Aim past it...
Reach through the sky...!
Attack him as though
your life depended on it!
Okay... I'll see what I can do.
Get ready you guys...
here goes!!
The power...!
It's amazing!!
I'm feeling faint...!
It's too much!
Got it!
Now let's finish this!
Infinity Punch!
Keep aiming for the sky!!!
It's amazing!
He actually did it!
So this is what Fudo meant...
The power of his thoughts,
and... his whole heart...
Just a little bit further!
He's reached it!
Don't fret, Otoha...
It's just another
crater on the moon.
Now that's...
shootin' for the moon...
Hi Reika.
Like flower petals fall,
love is laid to rest...
All things of
this world dissolve
into the vast
emptiness of darkness...
Evil resurrects
itself once again...
Next time on Aquarion:
"Knight of the Crimson Rose."