It's the vampire!
This is the end Reika! Hold me!
Get... off... of... me!
Stop acting like a
little girl, Pierre...
It's just a movie.
Silvia... try using
your imagination...
Isn't that right sweetness?
Hey! Quit groping!
Tough girl huh...?
Nothing scares you... right?
Did that vampire look
familiar to you guys?
I kept thinking I was
seeing Rena up there.
Jun, what's that...?
On your neck?
You've got two red marks...
Hate to tell you this, kid...
...but you've been
bit by a vampire.
Look Tsugumi!
You've got the same marks.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Calm down!
Deep breathes...
Please don't blow up!
Relax... They're tick bites.
What?
You can stop freaking out...
Ticks always
bite at least twice.
Okay then, there's no
such thing as vampires
and we can all just relax.
During the year of Holy Genesis,
great changes occurred
in the magnetic fields
of our planets...
These changes activated
many latent characteristics
usually hidden in the
genomes of human beings...
These characteristics
are the basis
for your abilities as elements.
Tsugumi?
Are you okay... Are you sick?
I don't know... I feel so dizzy.
Jun.
Someone call the
infirmary, immediately!
Unbelievable...
An anemic outbreak here...?
It just goes to show
they're not taking care
of themselves properly.
Maybe, but for two to get sick
at the exact same time...?
I should probably take
another look at our meal plans.
Water is the dark
mirror to all things.
Wait for it.
Demonic blood suckers...
or vampires.
These creatures of darkness date
all the way back
to ancient Greece...
...consumption of human blood...
provides them eternal life.
They're repelled by crosses and
garlic and invisible to mirrors.
Exposure to sunlight
burns them to dust.
The character of Count Dracula
was modeled after an actual
person,... Vlad Tepes...
Better known as,
"Vlad, the Impaler."
Impaler?
Could Rena be
related to this prince?
From what I see here,
that's entirely possible.
What's this?
Looks familiar.
Hold on...
Now that I think about it...
One time Rena drank
my blood like that...
So she must be a vampire.
I wonder who's next on her list?
I can't believe it...
She's so little and cute.
Hey, what is it, Tsugumi?
I remember... I was
pruning roses in the garden.
Are you okay?
Hi Rena.
She what?!
Seriously...
She's taken blood
from three of us...
Could she be draining
us little by little?
That accounts for the
sudden outbreak of anemia.
I remember something else!
I fell during a
training exercise
and Rena came out of nowhere.
Isn't it a possibility that
every time Rena takes blood
from us, she's taking
some of our Prana as well?
Our Prana...?!
Then she's no different
than the Shadow Angels!
Then that makes Rena the enemy?
Well... think about it.
Since vampires don't exist...
She's most likely
a shadow angel!
I see... she takes a
little blood at a time...
Secretly draining
our life force...
Reika.
Your gossiping makes me sick!
What are you talking about?
Silvia?!
Rena... Rena!
Apollo... Did Rena
come this way?
Huh?
You weren't looking for...
What are you doing?!
I was just looking
for something to eat.
Idiot!
What's the hell wrong with you?
Never mind!
For just a second,
I thought you might actually
be thinking about
somebody else for a change.
You're you and
that's all I care about.
It's so pure... music like that
comes straight from the soul.
Listen... her words are weeping.
You're an angel...
Will you sing
another one for us?
I got a question...
What's with the umbrella?
It's a nice day out.
Moron...! It's called a parasol!
It's a fashion accessory!
I'm sensitive to the sun.
Rena... why is it that
you're constantly avoiding us?
Rena?
This can't be you...
This picture's so old.
Suppose I said... It is me?
Careful, that's twice
you've hurt yourself.
Rena...! I was
actually looking for...
I can feel that
you're afraid of me.
The others are afraid as well...
That's why you're here?
That's not it...!
I just wanted to stop
everyone from gossiping.
I'm your friend.
It doesn't matter what
anybody else says...
I trust you!
Are you certain...?
Ask yourself.
Rena.
She still hasn't
come back... has she?
High-level quantum readings in
the vicinity of Lowland City...
Vectors, dispatch immediately.
Guys...?
Why is it getting so dark?!
Wait!
Where are they?
Probably hiding like cowards.
Are we close?
Come out already.
Where are you hiding?
Vitals summary...
Their pulses are rising.
Emotional auras
are shifting rapidly.
Fear and anxiety
are gaining control.
Commander...
their uncertainty
could undermine
Aquarion's potency.
Let's see.
Is that it...? I can't tell.
Could it be?
Rena's the enemy!
Now what?
She's a vampire
and a Harvest Beast!
No way!
Oh no.
Rena...?! Find Rena!
It's no use... she's either
not responding or out of range.
Because she's out there!
Isn't it obvious.
It can't be.
How could this have happened?
Stop. Don't come near me!
Silvia...! Do something!
But, Silvia was the one who
defended Rena.
And it's Rena that will
destroy her...! Defend yourself!
No wait!
Well we just can't stand here.
That's Rena you're fighting!
Question...! What should you do
if your friend becomes your foe?
Commander...? What does that-?
Sirius, tell me
what you would do?
I would kill them.
You think you'd be able to?
Do something...!
Rena's gonna slaughter us all.
Please! Rena no!
What's happening...!
What's she doing?
She's feeding...
Leeching Aquarion of its prana!
She's gaining strength.
Let go of me!
That's not Rena I'm smelling...
It stinks like harvest beast!
Rena, where are you?
Apollo!
Come back to us...?!
We need you...!
I know you can hear me!
That mongrel has lost his mind.
Ree--Naah!
Listen to me...
The time is now!
Apollo.
Show us who you
really are... Rena...
Your friends need you.
Come home!
Rena!
Reeeeenaaaaaah!
He calls.
It's Rena!
But... how is she there?
I don't know...
I sure didn't teleport her.
That's not possible.
It's some sort of trick.
Watch out, she'll kill you!
Welcome back.
Yep... It's you.
Rena...? How did you...?
Silvia.
I'm so sorry... I thought...
I know...
I can be very frightening... no
one knows that better than I do.
Rena.
And you...?
Why aren't you afraid?
What, like I don't know you?
C'mon.
Let's do this.
What?!
Merge one!
Merge two!
Go!
Aquarion!
Oh my.
This feels... so strange.
It's lovely.
Amazing.
It was.
It's coming.
Get up!
Their aura levels are way down!
Bio-energy dropping fast...!
They're too weak!
It's sucking our life force.
Rena!
It's taken...
all of my strength.
Okay...
Then you know
what we have to do.
Drink from my neck...
This is your fight;
you can do this!
Really...
Oh no you don't!
We're in this together!
Rena, you can have
some of mine too.
Silvia, thank you...
both of you.
Alright then, dig in.
I'm sorry.
Element's bio-levels restored...
Energy's climbing.
Now Aquarion...!
Rise up and regroup!
That a girl.
Now show that thing whose boss.
You're okay?
But she...
Hurry.
Silvia... I need you to help me.
You got it.
Know your true enemy...
Vampire... Silver Cross!
Mirrors that reflect darkness.
Shed light on the darkness that
lurks within all of our hearts.
The harvest beast itself
was merely a manifestation...
their true enemy was the
fear they carried inside.
Please forgive me...
There are times... when
the moon is at its fullest
that I lose all self control and
succumb to my primal urges...
I apologize if I upset anyone...
I guess you're welcome...
Rena your elemental
powers are unmatched.
ESP and vampirism...
I mean...
Ehhhh...
"Receiver and giver
of life force."...
Oh and I almost
forgot the teleportation.
I want to apologize, Rena.
Somehow I got it into my
head that you were the enemy.
We all did...
Our judgment was
clouded by fear...
You're forgiven...
But I'll gladly remove
any residual guilt
through two little
holes in your necks.
What!
You won't be needing ours
because Apollo said your
welcome to his any time.
Ah what?
And Rena, his blood's
always the hottest.
It's okay?
Why not? Not like
it hurts, right?
Wait a minute.
Can't too much of that
be bad for his health!
Sounds like someone's
a little jealous!
What? What are
you talking about...
That's absolutely ridiculous!
You know, if it's ridiculous,
why are being so defensive?
Shut your mouth! Tsugumi!
Whatever!
C'mon. He's cute. Admit it!
Oh yeah, maybe to somebody
like you, whose blind as a bat!
You're blushing.
I am not blushing! Shut up!
Silvia loves Apollo...
I do not!! Ugh!
Would you stop it?
You do! You do!
Ugh! Shut up!!
Reika, I can't handle
much more of this!
Yes you can, Tsugumi! Be strong!
It's not worth it!
Tsugumi!
Next on Aquarion:
"Merge to Eat."
I'm so hungry!