Glen.
'ey. Not too bad, Reika.
You're not so bad yourself.
This is all my fault,
if only I could have
held the merge...
Doctor!
Why does everything
near me suffer?
Look at the water!
Worrying helps no one.
Glen has always been strong.
He will pull
through this in time.
Reika?
What does that card symbolize?
The turning point of fate.
This is just great
now how are we supposed
to get back to the dorms?
I wonder whose bad luck
could have caused this?
Silvia!
Oh... Sir...
Your eyes are gifted with the
clarity of a bubbling spring.
Unfortunately, this water
cannot render any tea...
Not until the ripples of
fear and doubt have subsided
Sirius?
I was just wondering...
how's Reika related to
Aquarion in her previous life?
I don't know...
She's a mystery,
but she's certainly
one of the most gifted
elements in the group.
Yeah? Well that's funny,
because I clearly remember
Reika causing serious problems
on nearly all of our missions.
During our first trial,
Reika was entrusted
with piloting Aquarion...
...our merge was a
transcendent experience.
But Brother.
You wanna merge with
her a second time?!
Brother...
I'll have nightmares if I don't
sleep in your room tonight.
I suppose...
but just for tonight.
Reika, where are you?
Oh good you're back!
I'm glad you made it home okay!
It's ruined.
She's quite a lady.
Alright, this should do it...
Here it goes.
Okay... You're all set.
You're so awesome Jun.
You're really are.
Not really...
Reika, why don't you go
ahead and give it a try?
Who? Me...? Ah... I don't know.
Oh... go ahead.
It's okay,.
It's gonna work fine.
What the...?
A black out.
That's... impossible!
The monitor...
Stay away!
Make it stop!
You think those were ghosts?
No. No way...
There's no such thing.
Jun... I'm so sorry...
I ruined all your hard work.
No Jun, this is all the
result of my bad luck.
It's so early Reika...
What are you
doing out and about?
I tell ya, I can't catch
anything today...
Catch anything...?
Exactly... what were
you looking to catch?
I was trying to
find some protein.
Huh...? C'mon Apollo...?
There's plenty of food at DEAVA.
Yeah, but it's full
of preservatives.
Nothing's fresh,
all the flavors are dull.
Wait... you're telling
me you actually kill
wild animals and eat them raw?
Well, that was the
only way I could survive
before I got to this hole.
I'm sorry I ran into you...
if I'd stayed away you could
have caught something.
My presence only seems
to bring people bad luck.
What?
That's the most ridiculous
thing I've ever heard...
It was no more than
man versus beast out there
and this round
went to the beast.
Well I guess I stand corrected,
you did ruin my hunt after all.
I picked up your scent from
all the way in the valley...
I was so thrown off by it
I couldn't find a single mouse.
I see... The breeze
must have carried it off...
Hey, not too bad Reika...
Reika, the first
time I try to merge...
I'd really like
it to be with you.
Oh... and you too.
Not until the ripples of
fear and doubt have subsided.
High level quantum readings
are coming from Lake Oolong.
Sirius, Silvia, Reika.
Stand by, and prepare to launch.
Vector Mars, taking off!
Vector Luna, taking off!
Reika's not here!
I'm taking over!
Apollo???
This is totally unauthorized...!
Reika...? Where is Reika?!
I found this...
...on Reika's desk.
"Please don't come after me."
Prana energy? In the lake?
What???
Passengers,
please remain calm...
We are trying to determine
the reason for our stop...
For your safety,
please remain seated
with your seatbelts fastened.
I'm to blame for this.
Vectors.
My bad luck must
have brought them here.
My reason for leaving DEAVA
was to protect the others
from my curse...
Why's it still happening?
Please, make it stop.
I just don't get it...
I don't see any Cherubim.
I mean there's no
beast around here either.
I don't know about that.
Hey!
Something about that train...
Let's double back... Now!
Right.
I've got to get away
from here quickly.
They'll die.
The quantum levels at the lake
are skyrocketing.
Check last month's volume data.
There's been no rain for months,
and yet the lake's swelled
to five times its normal size.
That's impossible.
My suspicion is that a Harvest
Beast is hiding in the water.
All right then...
Vectors merge immediately
with Sirius as the head.
Roger!
I've got to get away...
before everyone suffers.
Aquarion!
What the--?!
What's wrong...? We can't merge.
What just happened?
Oh no.
Their merge shields
are completely disabled.
Forgive me.
It's so cold.
What...? Hold on...
I just checked
your cabin readings,
the temperature hasn't changed!
Sooooo, I wonder
what that's about...?
Hey Silvia, maybe
you're just cold hearted?
Shut your face!
You're looking much warmer now.
I'm not kidding.
It feels like I'm
freezing to death in here.
Can't... move...
I'm showing operational
systems failure
from all three Vectors sir...
They've lost control.
Well then shut up and fix it...!
We don't know how long
they can last down there!
My body is
completely immobilized.
They're in serious
danger Commander...
Please... you must
order a change.
We can't...
Their teleporters are
completely disabled.
What's the cause?!
It's unknown.
That scent?
The breeze must
have carried it off...
She's close.
Reika!
What the hell are
you doing out here?
Reika?
What's she doing?
What's going on?
Amazing.
You mean to tell me
that she's responsible
for this terrible mess we're in?
I'm so sorry...
I wanted to protect
you all from this.
I think there's something
at the bottom of that lake...
No...
Any effort from me will
only make things worse...
Get out of here Reika and
take your curse with you.
Forgive me!
Rieka!
Holy crap!
Look, there she is!
She's okay!
This is my bad luck again.
You call this bad luck...?
This is called life.
Life gets tough,
so you have to get tougher.
No, you're wrong.
You're all so blind...
It's my bad luck that's holding
you now, but you can't see it.
All right, fine...
You got a choice;
hold on to your shame...
Or find the courage to
face your fate head on!
My fate is inescapable.
So let's see just how
doomed I really am!
Sirius.
Sirius...
I'll come for you...
just hang on.
The lake now appears
to be changing its form.
It's doing what?
Quantum levels are
on the rise again...!
They've more than tripled!
I can move.
Those poor children...
They were crying
out to us for help.
They're still alive!
Reika!
Feelin' lucky yet...?
You call the shots now!
Okay, but consider
yourself warned.
That's the spirit...!
What's our plan?
The whole lake
has been possessed
by the harvest beast...
It's swallowing people,
then draining their
life force to serve its own.
It ate us?
I guess that means we're
stuck inside its belly, huh?
Well let's chew our way out.
Good idea.
Where's my brother?
Don't worry Silvia...
I'm not letting him go.
Reika.
There's not much time!
Look... The whole
lake's floating away.
I know...
We've gotta get
them out of there
before they're
gone for good!
Reika's quantum
levels are climbing...
Rapidly.
Her successful merge rate
is only 17.2 percent...
We can't risk a mistake!
The old pond is full, Reika.
Merge One!
Merge two.
Go Aquarion!
Reika?
This is so creepy!
Now transform all my fear, and
shame into Aquarion's power!
Reika.
I had no idea
you hurt so deeply.
Aquarion... Strike!
You've hit rock bottom...
now breakthrough!
Right! Let's Go!
It's time I foughtt back!
Unlucky Bottom Attack!
Good work.
Smells like victory.
Thank you so much...
Both of you.
Sure...
I'm just relieved
everyone was able
to make it through unharmed.
My brother... He's okay.
You should talk to him,
let him know that you
were able to merge again...
He'll be happier than
anyone to hear that.
Ya.
Glen?!
Tell me what happened to Glen.
Just give me a second.
He's been transferred to the New
United Nations Medical Center,
and right now his condition
appears to be unknown.
But Silvia...
I feel awkward
doing the preview.
Well don't...
You know everything you
do is executed flawlessly.
You think so?
Of course...
Next time on Aquarion:
"The Time of Amber."
Don't forget...
We'll merge next time too.