From Mimuro's mountain slopes, maple leaves are torn...
Which turn Tatsuta river...
Into a rich brocade...
Though it cost my life...
The same favored card as the Master, huh?
We now must meet...
All of this is because of you,
Momiji Ooka.
And as soon as today's program
is recorded, I should thank you.
Heh.
Huh? Faster than I'd thought you'd be.
Thanks for coming.
Huh?!
You're not..! What the hell are you doing?!
Stay away from me!
Wah... Agh...
Ugh!
In Naniwa Bay, a flower blooms, in winter...
Then spring will rise, and a new flower shall bloom...
Since I could bring no offering...
Woah... And the Karuta card goes flying...
Oh, don't bother.
O... kay?
Please, excuse me.
Beautiful!
Please dad! Keep your voice down!
She's so cute!
Like an idol!
And that kimono suits her!
So, uh, remind me, why exactly
are we watching a Karuta game?
That's a good question.
Hm?
Mikiko asked us to stay in the
waiting room until the interview starts.
But all of a sudden, you got distracted by a
pretty girl and followed her to the studio, remember?
Who is Mikiko?
I introduced you to her!
Take your eyes off Kimono girl. Mikiko's over there.
She's the chief of the Karuta
club I joined at Kaiho Academy.
Hold on a second.
You're in the Karuta club, Kazuha?
Yeah! You didn't know?
You guys went off to the bathroom hours ago!
Sorry. The studio door was shut and I
didn't know if we were gonna be allowed back in.
Uh, pardon me guys.
We're kinda in the middle of rehersal,
so could you maybe keep the noise down?
Right, sorry...
The wandering stag calls...
Once, my life was not dear to me...
Now I desire it shall endure...
Woah..!
Hohoh! Look at that throw!
Hey, Kudo.
What do you wanna bet, pops already
forgot he came down to Osaka for an interview?
If he has, it's forgivable.
Since Doc had something to do and couldn't make it,
Kogoro finally gave in to everyone's
nagging and brought them along.
And by the way, whatever happened to that rich girl?
Oh, you mean Sonoko?
She's sick in bed with a cold.
Aah...
I had no idea you liked that.
It's pretty cool you joined the Karuta club!
Yeah, Aikido and Karuta.
The Karuta club almost had to shut down, due
to lack of members, so I was happy to help out.
I went now and then to help Mikiko practice.
But otherwise I was pretty much a ghost member.
A ghost member? That's so funny.
I'm so glad you're both having such a good time.
Perhaps you two think this is a coffee house?
Huh... Sorry about that...
I'm Shinichi Kudo, a high school detective.
I went to an amusement park with my childhood friend Ran,
and while we were there, we witnessed
some men in black making a dangerous deal.
Because I was so absorbed in watching them,
I didn't notice the man who came at me from behind.
He forced me to drink a poison that
knocked me out. And when I woke up...
I discovered that my body had shrunk!
If those guys ever found out that Shinichi
Kudo is still alive, they'd come back.
So on Doctor Agasa's advice, I
kept my real identity a secret.
When Ran asked me who I was, I
quickly made up the name "Conan Edogawa."
I knew if I wanted info on the men in black,
the smart thing to do would be to
stay at her house with her and her dad,
who ran a detective agency.
Heiji Hattori. High school detective of the west.
His father's Chief of HQ with the Osaka Police,
and he's solved several cases with his inherited skills.
He's one of the few who know about my true identity.
Kazuha Toyama, is Heiji's childhood friend and classmate.
He can drive her up the wall with a single offhand remark.
I can't help but wonder how
those two are going to end up...
And finally, the future Karuta queen, a
brilliant card player shrouded in mystery.
My body may have shrunk, but my I.Q hasn't.
Detective Conan leaves no case unsolved!
There is always only one truth!
Aw, we came all the way out to a
studio just to sit in the waiting room?
I wanted to see the show!
They're never letting us back
in, they even got mad at Kogoro!
Sorry guys, I didn't mean to get us kicked out...
Hey, When everyone else gets back, Hm? what
do you say we go out looking for some souvenirs?
Yeah!
Really?
Seriously?
Sure. If you guys can behave until they finish filming!
Yeah, you bet!
That's awesome!
Everybode else should come too!
Hey, if we got kicked out, what happened to Conan?
Oh, Conan's in the studio.
He's looking after dad to keep him out of trouble.
I'm confused.
Huh?
I told you to go sit in the
waiting room, yet here you are.
You did, but Ran said she wanted me to
stay here so I could watch the filming!
Figures.
Make way, everyone! Karuta
cards coming through, clear a path!
It's the Satsuki Cup cards!
That's a lot of protection for some Karuta cards.
Well they're certainly deserving.
Those aren't just some cards...
They're the traditional deck of the
Satsuki Cup used in the final match!
Oh yeah! Right...
I guess competing in a contest
with those was your dream, huh?
Not just mine!
They've been adored for all of the
Satsuki Association's 20 year history!
Just touching those legendary cards in
the finals would be like a dream come true!
Hey!
Why are those particular cards only used in the finals?
They've been played in some
intense matches it's starting to show.
That's why when they're not being
used they're on display in a museum
stored safe and sound in a case like that one.
Maybe so, still seems like way
too much for a bunch of cards.
It does not!
Huh?
Actually right after last year's
tournament the cards went missing.
Thank goodness they were found right away but...
The grand champion, Mr. Yajima, convinced
President Achiwa greater security was needed.
I see. Now tell me...
Who exactly are these people you mentioned?
Heheh...
Are you serious?! They're the ones
you're here to interview in the first place!
Oh, is that a fact?
You never give an inch, do you?
The man in this photo is President Kensuke Achiwa.
Huh...
He founded Achiwa Real Estate,
and now he's known as the Real Estate King of Naniwa.
He doesn't strike me as a guy who likes playing Karuta...
Apparently it's his only hobby. He's
supposed to be pretty good at it, too.
But I've seen articles about how he wanted
to be a reader of cards instead of a contestant.
Wohohohohoah! Who is that?!
President Achiwa's wife, Satsuki.
Ah, so she's married, huh?
She sort of established the Satsuki
Association and used to be the queen.
Mister Achiwa took after her and became president.
Okay, and what else might come up in the interview?
Ah, this could be interesting right?
Whenever his wife enters an important competition,
Mr. Achiwa always washes his car.
It says here he thinks it brings him good luck.
According to him a clean car is the first step to victory!
You're telling me I have to do an interview
with this superstitious weirdo couple?
Well...
Huh?
Not exactly the both of them. About three
years ago, Satsuki got sick and passed away.
Your interview today will just be with President Achiwa.
I, uh... I see...
Who's this super strong looking guy?
He's in almost every one of
these pictures with Mr. Achiwa...
Togo Kaeda.
Huh?
He used to be Mr. Achiwa's secretary.
Rumor has it he ran the shady
side of the real estate empire.
He's really clever. But it seems he quit and disappeared.
Heiji!
Huh?
That is completely an unfounded rumor!
There is no way Mr. Achiwa's a criminal!
Take it back!
Okay, okay.
I said it was just a rumor?
The president's coming!
Huh?
President Achiwa! Let's go say hi!
It's an honor to have you with us today Mr. President.
The pleasure's all mine, thanks so much for having me.
Yes, sir.
I believe that Mr. Yajima and Momiji are
going to perform a little demonstration.
And then there's an interview to follow?
That's right, and we're going to air the film we
shot of Mr. Yajima's demonstration from last week.
After that, we'll show a Satsuki
Association special that will
hopefully get the whole nation excited about Karuta again.
Oh, I see the Satsuki Association's
cards are already on display.
Is everything going to plan?
Of course!
He draws in the whole room!
Well, what else would you expect from real estate royalty?
Excuse me, but can anyone get a hold of Mr. Yajima?
It's his call time and I just can't
find him anywhere! I've tried everything!
How strange,
he promised us he'd be here an
hour before we were set to air.
Yajima wouldn't be this late, it's simply not like him!
But just to have assurances, give Mister Sekine a call.
If worse does come to worst, I'm
sure he can serve as a substitute.
Huh..?
No... There's no way..!
There's some time before filming.
A little bit.
So Heiji! Where do you wanna take us for lunch?
To the #1 spot for Okonomiyaki, of course!
I think I know just where you're talking about!
Woah!
Uh...
I'm so sorry, are you all right?
Hey, you were the one playing Karuta!
It's destiny.
Huh?!
Something told me that I would get to see you!
My future husband... I've missed you so!
Future- what?!
Your husband?!
Huuh?!
I'll have some free time right
after we're done filming, my darling.
Why don't we go out for a cup of tea? Get reacquainted!
Just what do you think you're doing?!
I swear! I wasn't gonna...
Miss Momiji!
Huh?
Please Miss, I need you to get back to the waiting room!
Oh, well it's such a shame I have to leave so soon.
The thing is, Mr. Yajima is
running just a little late right now.
That's not like him...
After all he did to make sure this
program goes off without a hitch...
I'm certain he's just tying up loose ends.
I'll come and see you as soon as we're done, Heiji!
Okay, I'll be waiting!
Ugh!
Just who the hell is that girl?
She was the pretty girl playing Karuta!
She's adorable!
I think her name was Momiji.
I told you, I don't even know the girl!
Then how did she know your name huh?
Hey Ran?
Let's go wait outside!
We'll come back when they're done arguing.
Come on let's go!
I wonder what she's so mad about?
REAL friendly!
Well, I guess... Maybe we met somewhere before?
Oh, of course, I see! So you do know her.
Look, I told you I don't.
And trust me, because I'd never
forget someone as beautiful as that girl.
Do you really think she's beautiful..?
You're memorable too but, y'know, for different reasons.
Excuse me?! Just what do you mean by that?
Hold on.
Are you really saying you don't know who she is, Heiji?
Momiji Ooka?
Apparently she's the Satsuki Cup
high school champion two years in a row.
She's a junior at Kyoto Senshin High School.
People say she'll be the Karuta Queen one of these days.
Momiji Ooka?
She must be incredible...
So this is the threat we received this morning?
It just says here that Nichiuri TV will be bombed.
What's this Image of a Karuta card about?
It was attached to the bottom of the email.
We still haven't figured out what it means.
Has Nichiuri TV been informed
of the threat against them yet?
They have. We sent them a notice.
What do you think, Heizo?
Is this message an honest to goodness
threat or just some stupid prank?
It's difficult to tell from just the one email.
But if this threat is real, it'll be a disaster.
An emergency evacuation alert has been
issued, by the Osaka Prefectural Police.
They want to evacuate the building?
and evacuate,
Hm? What in the...?
Is this some kind of fire drill?
Do you know what's happening Ran?
They mentioned the police.
Think they're filming another program?
Please stop all operations and filming,
and evacuate via the emergency stairs...
You! Find out what's going on!
Yeah... Right!
Sounds like we'd best make our way out.
Kazuha, I need you to get to
the emergency stairway. Stay safe.
Wait! What about you?
I'm gonna go find out what's happening
here. You clear out of the building, okay?
But! Heiji!
What the-?
Hey! You're supposed to be heading outside!
I forgot something in the studio!
I don't care! Didn't you hear
that announcement they just made?!
Ugh...
Apologies, my lady.
I was surprised as well...
I really wish I'd had some time to change...
Heheh.
This is real bad! We need everyone out of here!
Calm down. What happened?
The cops say there's a bomb threat on the building!
What?! President Achiwa!
I'm certain this is just a prank, sir.
But just to be safe, we should evacuate.
Precautions must be taken.
All right people, you heard the announcement!
Let's get everyone outside! Hurry up!
All right! Got it!
Mikiko, what are you doing?!
Huh?!
It's too dangerous here. We have to go!
Sir, come on!
Huh?!
Woah!
What're you doing? Let's move!
Everyone, keep moving in an orderly fashion.
We just need to make sure it's safe before we
Everybody, stay where I can see you, we let you all
back into the building. until it's safe to go back in.
Great, even more waiting.
I can't get a signal...
Dad's still inside but I'm sure he can find a way out.
Ran!
Hey, it's Dad and Conan!
What the heck is going on in there?
Some kind of surprise fire drill or something?
It's not, I asked the staff
about it when we first came out.
They said there'd been a bomb threat.
Are you serious?!
Wait, where's Kazuha and Heiji?
Hold on! I thought they came outside with you!
No. I'm gonna head inside and look for them
No! I'll go.
Wait right here and don't move!
Hear me?!
Hmm...
Couldn't have picked a worse time for an evacuation drill.
If this is a joke, it's not funny!
Heiji! Mikiko!
Come on! We gotta go!
Sorry, I was worried about you two, that's all!
I'm so sorry!
I can't leave those cards behind! I'm going back for them!
Huh?!
If I can find the GPS location...
You're kidding, Hattori is still inside! For real?!
You! What're you doing?!
Forget the cards! You need to evacuate!
Listen!
Mikiko!
Huh?
What are you guys doing here?!
Do you have any idea what kind of danger you're in?!
I'm sorry!
Ah! Yeah, me too!
Come on...
Found a few in Studio Three.
Mikiko!
You had me so worried!
Get them out!
Roger that!
I'm really sorry, I just couldn't help myself!
I mean, if it was a real bomb threat...
It could blow any second,
we'll fall back and observe
until we deem it safe to approach!
That's good thinking.
There were 3 left in the studio
but they're being evacuated, sir.
They were the last, yes?
Right!
All right. Now that the civilians are safe,
it's up to us to find that bomb. Let's go!
Yes, sir!
The police went inside...
No way it's just a prank...
Come on, hurry! This way.
It was real!
Everyone, get out of here!
Yes, sir!
Expand the perimeter, get everyone back!
Keep the civilians away!
Keep moving, sir!
Woah!
Look out!!
Kazuha!
Woah...
No! Stay here where it's safe.
Damn it! Where the hell are they?!
I hope Hattori's not injured... or worse!
Kazuha!
Ah!
Stop! It's dangerous!
Come with me!
Ah..!
Are you all right? Can you walk?
Y-Yes.
Good! Let's go. This way!
The building could collapse. We can't risk going in...
Right...
Keep it moving, folks!
There were people still inside?
What?!
Go! Go!
Argh!
Gah!
Heiji!
Ah, close one...
Run! Get away!
We can't go down...
Kazuha, we're going up!
What do you mean? That's the way out!
We can't get out there, so let's
find somewhere we can breathe!
Don't tell me...
He's going up?
Damn. It's not going through...
Go, go!
Kazuha! Come back!
Oh... This is bad... The whole roof's gonna collapse!
More! Get as close as you can!
This is the closest we're going to get!
Excuse me! Coming through!
Damn! I can't see anything in this smoke.
No way I can handle this. Not by myself!
Kudo!
It's do or die.
Let's do this.
Haah!
Let's go!
That's him!
Took you long enough..!
Argh.
Ah! Ugh...
Hah!
Hattori!
Wait, where are we going?
To the only way out of this place, come on!
Down? That's crazy!
Wait here, I'll be right back!
Heiji! We'll never make it, it's too high!
Hey, I'm ready when you are!
Same here. There's no more time to waste!
Right!
Ah..
Here we go!
This is a bad idea! I can't see a thing now! Wait! Heiji!
Hang tight and keep your eyes closed, okay?
Huh?! Hey, wait a sec!
No!
No no no, put me down!
I owe you one, we'll be waiting down below!
I gotcha.
What are you doing?
No... What are you?!
Ugh!
Kudo!
Ah! Damn!
It can't be!
Everybody see that?! Come on!
That's Heiji!
There is somebody there!
Go and get the stretcher!
Huh?
Kazuha!
Ah.. Huh... Heiji...
Damn. That was the only way to get down...
Come on, think! There's got to be another way out of here.
A rescue chopper!
No, that's no good... With all the fire and
smoke they'd never be able to get close enough...
But wait! There's that river next to the station.
If I can get over there...
Here goes!
Ugh...
Not enough room to get my skateboard up to speed.
Woah!
Just breathing makes it feel like my lungs are on fire!
I've gotta do something and fast!
Gotta... try..!
Ugh...
No!
I won't give up... No matter what!
There's gotta be somewhere I can build up some speed.
There's gotta be!
That'll work!
You're low on time, Kudo! Hurry up!
Huh?!
Woah, that's him!
I mean it's gotta be! But what the heck's the plan?
Huh?
The river! Clever as always.
A little more...
A little faster...
I can barely breathe.
But I'm almost there!
Woah!
It's gonna fall!
I sure hope this works!
Damn, not enough speed!
Gah!
I'm not gonna make it!
Gah! Augh!
Hup!
I gotcha! Come here!
Hey, are you okay?!
I'm all right, yeah.
Here, you dropped these.
Thanks.
Did you know that Nichiuri TV was gonna be bombed?
Is that why you brought that thing?
No, of course not! It was just a coincidence.
I like to keep it around for emergencies.
There's always an emergency when you're around.
Ahah... You have a point.
Kazuha!
Hey, Ran!
Are you all right?
Yeah, but, my memory's fuzzy...
I think I must have inhaled a lot of smoke or something.
As long as you're okay, that's what matters.
Glad it turned out alright.
Yeah.
Oh, and I think I dropped the car key
somewhere, so I'm gonna go take a look for it.
Okay, Dad!
By the way, where's Conan?
I assumed this is the evacuation center he would come to.
Hey look!
Yay, it's Conan!
We were worried sick!
Woah, Kazuha!
Well, look who it is! And where have you been hiding?
Oh, I uh...
And what about you, Conan? We
were all worried sick about you!
I'm really sorry.
What happened to Mikiko?
Her arm was injured while they were escaping
the building so she was taken to the hospital.
Is she okay?
I hope it's nothing serious.
I found out what hospital she's
at. We can go see her if you like?
Yeah, let's go!
Heiji!
Inspector Otaki!
I'm so glad you're okay!
Go on, I'll be sure to catch up with you guys in a bit.
What?
Two seconds, I promise.
Ugh...
Let's go, Ran.
Okay... Come with us, Conan.
A-All right.
Let's leave them to talk, okay?
Yeah...
I'll see ya later, Conan!
So, is it true the police got word of a bomb threat?
This is the threat email sent
to our offices earlier today.
These are images of Karuta cards.
We believe those images must be somehow related
to the demonstration they were planning to film.
Why else would they attack Nichiuri TV?
It'll probably be a while before I can
get a chance to take a look inside, huh?
It will...
What the hell is this guy after?
Thank you very much, Doctor.
Of course, take care.
How'd it go in there?
Oh, it was nothing really, just a light scratch is all.
Thank goodness...
I can't believe such a tragedy could
happen right before the competition...
I know... Truly I am as shocked as you are.
Unfortunately, this disaster may force
us to cancel the Satsuki Cup this year.
No, you can't!
We have to play! We need to show
the public this hasn't broken us!
That's all well and good, but the cards we have always
used for the finals were destroyed the in the explosion.
If that's your only fear, then you needn't worry! - Huh?
The cards are safe!
Huh? But, how?!
What are you talking about?
Ms. Hiramoto took the Satsuki
deck with her when she evacuated.
M-Mikiko saved them?!
And we really are fortunate.
Because if they'd been destroyed
we'd have no choice but to...
Tell me! Are you absolutely
certain the cards are all right?
Yes! Someone from the museum took them
back. They wanted to check for smoke damage.
They're fine! You don't have to
worry about them! You can rest easy.
Yes... Yes, that is truly wonderful news, indeed.
But, where is Mikiko? I'd like
to thank her for her quick thinking.
She was injured escaping the building.
Huh?
I believe she's still in with the doctors...
I see.
It's taking a really long time...
The doctor said he was just gonna give her
first aid, so I hope it's not that bad...
Huh?
Mikiko! Don't tell me your arm is...
Yeah. It was broken when the roof caved in.
Maybe it's right I should be punished...
Mikiko...
No... I put you and Heiji in danger
when I went back for those cards and...
That's not true!
I am very proud of what you did in there.
Those cards you saved are the
face of the Satsuki Association.
I do not know that I can ever thank you enough,
but know that you have the gratitude of all of us.
Of course, sir. I'm just sorry
I can't play with a broken arm...
Yes. It is truly a shame that
a player of your exceptional
talent and skill won't be able
to show the world what you can do.
However, recovery should be your first and only priority.
He's right!
You can always compete next year!
Next year's too late.
Huh?
If we don't place well enough in the Satski Cup
this year, then the Karuta Club will have to shut down.
I can't let that happen... I just can't...
President.
Huh?
The officers are ready to head out, sir.
If you are.
Of course...
It's all gonna be okay.
I don't know...
I mean, its true that there's no one else in the club that
would stand a chance aside from you or I but maybe we...
That's it!
You have to do it!
Huh?!
You can play and represent Kaiho Academy in my place!
That's a little sudden, Mikiko!
But you've never played competitively before, have you?
No, never!
You always came to practice with me though, didn't you?
Y-Yeah.
You're strong and have great reflexes!
You're totally fearless and relentless
and you always keep calm under pressure!
Uuh...
Plus you're infuriating! It's perfect!
I'm not exactly sure that's a
compliment the way you think it is...
When is the competition supposed to be?
Er... They're supposed to play the day after tomorrow...
What?
You'll be okay! We'll use all the
time we have for nonstop training!
You really think an amateur has
any hope of winning the Satsuki Cup?
Karuta may be a bit complex for you,
perhaps a game of Go Fish would be better?
Don't patronize her!
We've practiced together all the time!
I know Kazuha has what it takes to win!
She might not be experienced,
but she's a top tier competitor!
Oh... I remember you now.
You were the girl who ws standing
at Heiji's side before, weren't you?
Though I am curious who you are to him.
Huh?!
I've known him since we were
little kids! Heiji's just my...
He's just my...
You like him!
Yeah, it's pretty obvious.
You're so in love!
Adults are talking now!
No one would ever know of my love for you...
Huh?
So you fancy yourself as that poem?
Isn't that adorable.
Er...
Then I supposed this is how it must be.
Whosoever should win this competition
shall also win Heiji's love all for herself.
She alone earns the right to confess her heart to him.
Uh oh...
What do you say?
Hold on, you cannot be serious!
If your love is true then I believe that's
something worth fighting for, isn't it?
Kazuha, listen. You don't have to do this, okay?
And just so you know.
I don't plan on losing to you.
Hold it!
Hm?
I accept your challenge!
You must be joking!
She's not!
You're passionate! I just hope you
can keep that up for the competition.
I'll be fine! How about you just focus on yourself, okay?
Actually, I think I'll go and do just that.
I was hoping to drop by the nail salon and maybe
think about how I'm going to tell Heiji my feelings!
Huh?
Um...
She looks a lot scarier now.
Yeah.
She's really confident!
Wow, that was incredible! Way to
give that girl a piece of your mind!
I guess so.
But I have no idea what I was thinking.
Huh?
Ah!
Woah, oh!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's my fault.
Dad, did you find the car key?
Not exactly...
I looked for it everywhere but, no luck.
Really, Dad?
I guess I'll just have to get a spare made.
Huh? What's up, Conan?
Momiji must've dropped this when they ran into each other.
Oh no! Here, let me see it.
Yeah, it's hers all right.
I'm gonna go give this back to her!
Hm, wait a sec!
This is terrible. What the heck am I supposed to do?!
Why are you asking me?
She was a little bit scary.
She was so beautiful though!
If she tells Heiji she likes him,
he's gonna fall head over heels for...
But she's no match for you, Kazuha! Not by a mile!
Really?
Yeah, totally!
Well, there's no use worrying about it now.
It's time gotta buckle down and start training!
Never been to a hospital before!
It's so big I feel like I might get lost in it!
Hey Ran! She's right over there!
Momiji! Hold on for a second! You dropped your train pass!
Momiji!
Aw, I was too late... What do we do now?
Well, we know her name and her school?
Hey, see if there's anything else inside!
Okay.
Do you mind if I take a look at it too?
Sure!
Let's see, she's got this picture in here?
Huh?Who is that man?
Oh, looks like there's one more.
Wow!
It's a picture of her when she was little.
It's Momiji and...
Is that Hattori?
They're pinky swearing!
Uh... Think they're promising to get married?
Like Heiji would be that lucky!
Come on, Conan! They're just kids!
You're right, that is silly.
Except I could totally see him doing that.
He'd totally do that.
Huh? It's Heiji's motorcycle!
Let's agree not to mention the photo, okay?
And especially not to Kazuha.
Yep.
Hey! You guys the welcoming committee?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Ran. So did you manage to catch up to her?
Uh, yeah!
Oh, hey!
Where have you been?
Hm?
Did you find out anything interesting?
No, the Osaka police are in total chaos.
Inspector Otaki says he'll get in touch as
soon as they find anything worth looking into.
Excuse me, I really think you should take this
call. It sounds like it's actually rather urgent.
Yes, of course I will.
That girl.
If it's not one thing then it's another with her.
Hello, from the Kyoto Prefectural Police Department.
Huh?
Right, okay. And what about, Mr. Yajima?
He was... He was murdered?!
Come on.
Right!
Hey, wait! Wait for me!
Thank you.
Hey you two, this area is off limits.
Right of course it is, but I'm here with Kogoro Mori.
Yeah, I don't think so.
They're alright, let them on through.
Y-Yes, sir.
Long time no see, you two.
Ah!
Inspector Ayanokoji!
The victim is Mr. Toshiya Yajima.
He's the son of a distinguished
family and he lived here all by himself.
He most likely died at around 6AM.
But the corpse wasn't found until 2 in the afternoon.
Oh, and you'll want to be careful where you step.
The killer ransacked the place.
Y-Yeah.
A robbery?
Huh?
If it was, it's safe to say it
didn't go as planned by the looks of it.
That was our analysis as well.
The murderer likely came in planning to rob
the place, but they ran into Mr. Yajima instead.
The killer beat him to death with
the sword he was about to steal.
Then he took the money and made his escape.
Poor man... But why?
The victim was practicing Karuta,
Huh? at the time of the attack.
Well observed.
Woah! Hey! What the heck are you two doing here?!
Hey there Inspector! We're just gonna
take a little look around if that's okay.
Forensics has already finished, so have at it.
You're kidding me...
Unfortunately we're gonna have
to take the murder weapon with us.
No problem, go right ahead.
Please stay with the kids until
they're done with their investigation.
Sir!
I'll be waiting for you just outside, so
let me know if there's anything you might need.
Right.
So what do you think?
There's a whole lot to process
here. Look at his right hand...
Yeah, you noticed the blood stains too?
Uh-huh. He must have been holding
something that was already stained.
There's only one thing in the room that's pretty bloody...
The Karuta cards.
The murderer must have noticed he was holding a
certain card and tried to hide it amongst the others.
It's gonna be tough to find which one in particular.
Well, maybe not.
Hm?
I think I might know someone who can help us.
Huh? Hold on.
Based on the blood stains, that remote
must've been really close to the victim.
Excuse me. Is it cool if I stand this TV up?
Sure, go ahead.
Thanks.
If he had the remote in his hands
until just before he was killed...
What was he watching?
Momiji Ooka?
So he was watching a Karuta match before he died...
Huh?
Hm? What did you find?
It looks like a match from a while ago...
Yeah.
It says it's, "The 15th to the 20th
High School Satsuki Cup Competitions."
I wonder why Yajima would have been watching it...
The finals are known for a very high standard of gameplay.
Just watching a player's techniques or the way the cards
are lined up can be an incredibly educational experience.
Of course, I doubt it has anything
to do with the murder, though.
Wait, but...
But nothing!
Shut up, come on you two!
Ugh- Pops wait!
You're done playing detective!
We'll get out of your hair! Thank you!
Uh... Very well.
Hmm...
And now for the news. Today at around 1:00 PM...
This news story again?
It's all pretty scary isn't it?
Hey! I was watching that, why would you turn it off?
Every time the news gets scary, you get
anxious and I don't want you to have a breakdown.
I suppose...
You did get in touch with the children, didn't you?
I've been trying but Shinichi
still hasn't called me back yet!
Oh?
Huh?
Well, right on cue. See?
Lovely. I can talk to him when you're finished.
Yeah.
It's about time. What were you thinking
not calling us as soon as you were safe?
Doc was really worried about you.
Yeah, sorry. It's been a little busy around here...
So, what did you call for?
I just emailed you a few photos a little while ago.
I want you to take a look at
the Karuta cards on the floor.
Huh?
First a bomb at the TV station,
and now blood-smeared Karuta cards?
I was hoping you could identify which
of those cards our victim was holding.
The boring stuff's your forte right?
Huh? Hmph.
You're boring.
Huh? There's a picture of a person in here.
Yeah, I'd like you to check out him too.
Is he a Karuta player?
I'm pretty sure he is.
I'll see what I can do. Give me a little time.
Thanks, I'm counting on you!
See ya!
Wait a second!
Doc wants..!
Ooh...
It's starting to look like they're intentionally
targeting members of the Satsuki Association.
Yeah, there's at least two potentials.
I can watch Mr. Achiwa. He's
staying at the same hotel as us.
And I'll keep an eye on Momiji Ooka.
Huh?
Stop right there! What are you doing here?
I'm a member of the Association, I have to get in!
Stay right there, sir! I'll need to see some verification.
There you are!
Huh?
Where the hell have you been, Sekine?!
I must have had you called hours ago!
I am so sorry, sir!
I kinda went out drinking last night,
must've overdone it and passed out
before I got my phone plugged in and charged.
Seriously?
And then when I woke up I saw the news about the
explosion down at the station. I called the association
and they said you were at Yajima's looking for me.
I rushed over, but it is absolute chaos getting here, sir.
What's with all the cops? Is... Is everything all right?
I'm afraid that... Mr. Yajima has been murdered.
Wait, what?!
It seems that he was attacked by a thief. And
was killed with the sword he kept in the hallway.
The katana... Oh god.
Mr. Achiwa, who is this?
Sorry, Inspector.
I work as a cameraman for the Satsuki Association.
The names Koji Sekine.
And also, Mr. Yajima's foremost rival.
As a matter of fact, they faced off against each
other in the finals of the last two competitions.
And I couldn't pull off the win in either one. I
was really hoping that this was gonna be my year...
Guess I'll never get my rematch now, huh...
So after everything that's happened today,
do you still plan to hold the competition?
Well to be perfectly honest, I
have no idea what we should do.
Sir, you can't be serious!
Just think about how it would
look! Yajima was just beaten to death!
There's no way you can call it off after
that. He would insist that we play on!
You might want to watch what you say, Mr. Sekine.
Sorry... Didn't mean to overstep...
I'm Inspector Ayanokoji, detective with the Kyoto Police.
If you have a moment, there are
few questions we'd like to ask.
Yeah, of course. What ever you need.
This way, please.
Uh, yes sir.
Well Inspector, if we're done here, I think,
Hey Kudo,
I think I know who the perp is.
So do I.
Koji definitely killed Mr. Yajima.
But what we don't have yet is a trace of evidence
that can tie him to the bombing of the station,
targeting the Satsuki Association.
Not yet.
But I think you're on the right track with
Achiwa and Momiji Ooka. We should keep tabs on them.
Yeah.
First place!
Second!
No fair! Wait for me!
Wow, look at this place! It's incredible!
Sonoko made the reservation.
But, I think it's because she wanted to come too.
There's no way we would have been able to
book somewhere this close to the station.
Only the best for Suzuki Financial.
That's right, thank you.
She'll be practicing all night,
so grab her some midight snacks.
Thanks for everything.
Aw man. Why do I do all this stuff for them?
I really enjoyed watching you go
all out rooting for your friends...
I guess it's okay.
Let the training begin!
Hey, we wanna help out!
So if there's anything we can do, just let us know!
Cause we've got your back Kazuha!
How sweet!
You guys are great.
Huh?
That's me.
Who's calling you?
Oh it's from Doc!
Oh!
I want to talk to him, too!
Yeah, let's all get on the call!
Okay, we're gonna take this!
You guys start training, we'll be right back!
We'll go over there so we don't bother you!
This is, totally got my back, huh?
They mean well.
There, I can see you now! Is
everybody all right after what happened?
Yeah!
We're A-Okay!
We're at the hotel now!
Well! That's good timing.
Huh?
Oh no.
Ta-daa! It's time!
To play Doc's quiz corner!
Is that really why you called us?
Here goes!
Karuta is a game where you race
to pick up cards off the ground.
And that movement is strikingly
similar to what traditional,
Japanese activity?
One: Picking tea leaves. Two: Flying a kite.
Three: Pounding mochi. Or four: Harvesting rice.
Grabbing cards is like picking tea so maybe the first one?
Maybe... It's flying a kite?
You do slap the cards down like pounding mochi?
I need your final answer!
Four, harvesting rice.
That's cheating, Ai!
Grabbing the cards looks very
similar to picking rice in a field.
She's right!
I get it!
Wah? Huh?
You know what? You're no fun!
Woah!
Hey you guys,
Don't stay up too late just
because you're on a trip, okay?
Okay!
I'm hanging up now.
Bye!
I didn't realize how late it was!
Dad and the others are running late...
I wonder if Heiji is still with them too?
If you're worried about him, then why don't you just call?
Uh, maybe I should...
Hm?
Hey! What's up, Kazuha?
What does that mean?
Huh?
Where could you be this late at night?
What? You're where?!
In Kyoto..?
Sorry. I've got some stuff to take care of.
You should probably head on home without me.
You can't be serious! I thought you
could help me with my Karuta training...
Your training?
I'm entering the competition.
Someone has to take Mikiko's place.
You've never played at that level before, have you?
Which would be why I'm training, dummy.
You were really good at Karuta way
back when you were a kid, remember?
Now that you mention it, I do remember playing in
elementary school, but that was just for fun, though.
You came out of nowhere and won
the whole thing! I was so surprised!
Well I don't know if I remember that happening...
Maybe not, but I definitely do!
When Mikiko asked me to join, the very first
thing I thought about was you winning that contest.
Oh? Cool.
Huh?
Well anyway, I've got some stuff
going on here, so I gotta split.
What the hell's wrong with you!?
Huh?Are you really that desprate
to get off the phone with me?
Pretty sure, that's not what I said?
You know what, go. I'll be fine without you.
Wait, what's wrong?
You idiot! Just go already!
Huh?
How is that boy so infuriating?!
What the hell is up with that girl?
Guess I can try to help...
Hey, it's me. I've got a little favor to ask.
Exactly, heh... Thanks.
Oh man, I'm exhausted.
Look who made it back!
When you guys roped me into coming here,
I had no idea there'd be a case involved.
Ugh...
Uh, Dad... Where's Conan?
I don't know.
I gave him a ride back to the hotel but,
As soon as we got in, he decided he
needed to talk to Mr. Achiwa right away.
Huh? Wow... Wonder what he's up to.
If Koji's really the perp, Mr. Achiwa
probably won't be targeted tonight.
Hm...
Huh?
Is everything okay, Ran?
Are you finished yet?
Uh, sort of?
Then, hurry back to the room, okay?
I mean, with everything going on I...
Right.
Gotcha, on my way!
Perfect. Now I can keep track of him even if he heads out.
Huh?
Isn't that..?
What's she doing here?
Our sleeves were wet with tears...
Hup!
Woah! Ah..
Wow! She's really good!
I don't think I can be your partner...
Watch where you're tossing those
things! You could've killed me!
I'm back!
Hey Conan!
And I brought along an excellent assistant.
Huh?
What?
Who's she?
Huh? That's Heiji's mother...
Heiji told me about you, so I decided to lend a hand.
But, why?
Oh uh... Hmm.
Huh?
It sounds like you need some help.
I hear you've been practicing Karuta.
Yes ma'am, but...
I shall serve as your partner.
Though a former queen like
myself may not be much assistance.
Former queen?
This is a favor for my son.
And for him I will be happy to
teach you all I know about the cards.
But since there isn't much time to
waste, I will not be going easy on you.
Will you accept my help?
Yes. I'll learn anything you can teach!
I thought you'd come, Inspector Ayanokoji.
We think alike. Great minds often do.
Guess so.
The little detective has decided
not to join you this evening?
He's busy keeping tabs on Mr. Achiwa.
Oh, I see. The two of you make quite the team.
Honestly, I'm starting to think
I got the raw end of this bargain.
When I volunteered, I didn't think Miss
Ooka would be living in a freaking mansion.
Hm?
Huh?
Uh...
It's lovely weather this evening.
It... certainly is...
Pardon, my name is Iori, and I am the
personal servant of Miss Momiji Ooka.
Hm...
I thought you might enjoy a cup of tea.
You must have been worried about me.
My future husband.
Though wet through and wet again,
do not so change their colors...
Oh, no!
Guess he hasn't left the hotel yet...
The waves are gathered...
You're pretty good.
I thought you would have given in ages ago, Kazuha.
Why don't we take a short
break, and you can get some rest?
No... Let's keep going!
Training requires rest.
I believe I'll go downstairs and get something to eat.
Ah... Kazuha!
Are you okay?
Let her sleep a while.
She's been training with all she has.
And, how did she do?
Far better than I anticipated.
I don't doubt that she'll make it into the top
four. But reaching the finals is another matter entirely.
Oh, no.
Don't worry yet. There is still much we can do.
I said it would be difficult but I didn't say impossible.
The most important things in competitive
Karuta are mental strength and concentration.
She has both.
If she focuses on the game, and the
game alone, I believe she could win.
I can't show this to her then...
She'd never get it out of her head.
This will be over soon, so please be patient.
Yeah, I can try, but frankly I've got somewhere to be.
So come on, what do you guys actually want from me?
I have some questions about Mr. Yajima's murder.
It... was a robbery gone wrong, right?
Or was it?
Huh?
My powers of deduction reveal,
this was premeditated murder.
Hang on!
Look, Yajima was a jerk, everybody knows that.
Even still, I can't imagine
anyone wanting to kill the guy?
Well, what about you?
That's crazy! Why the hell would I do that?
Mr. Sekine.
Huh?
You've lost the Satsuki Cup for two years in a row.
Both times to Mr. Yajima in the finals.
If he were suddenly out of the picture...
Then you would...
Then I would what? Cut the crap!
Yes of course I want to win!
But that sure as hell doesn't mean I'm gonna
go around killing everyone who's ever beaten me!
Besides, the police said it was a robbery! So back off!
Let me walk you through it.
Huh?
First, the way the house was ransacked was inconsistent.
What he means is the robber didn't
touch anything that was connected to Karuta.
The guy just killed someone. You really
think he's gonna be acting rationally?
Maybe not.
Or maybe the killer loved Karuta. So much so that he
couldn't bring himself to damage the cards in any way.
You detectives sure do come up
with some wild ideas don't you?
But, go ahead and feel free to
make up whatever story you like.
Uh...
Guess away!
Doesn't change the fact that I'm innocent. Crap!
Th-There's one more thing!
Yeah? What's that?
That floor of the hallway. It creaks.
Or maybe you don't remember. It's actually pretty loud.
Okay?
So loud in fact...
I don't think anyone could
enter without Mr. Yajima knowing.
And yet, but body showed no signs of any struggle.
I see. You're trying to say the intruder
must have been an acquaintance of Yajima's.
But you're wrong there. Even during
practice, a deep concentration is essential.
In that state, hearing anything
but the reader is next to impossible.
And that is the simple truth. Yajima
didn't notice until it was far too late.
Wrong again.
The blow that killed Mr. Yajima
was in the middle of his head.
If he didn't notice anyone coming
in and he continued to play...
The wound would've been on the
back of his head. Or perhaps the side.
In other words, unless Mr. Yajima knew his killer,
he would never have had the wound he did.
So here are the facts as they
stand. He wouldn't have a solid alibi,
he'd have to know Yajima and about Karuta...
Moreover, it must have been someone
who would benefit from his demise.
Hmm... It sounds like I fit the bill perfectly.
But, it's just speculation. There's no evidence.
If you wanna pin this murder on me,
you're going to need a lot more than that.
Hm?
Excuse me, Mr. Sekine? It's time to go!
Yeah, I'm coming!
You heard the man. Your time's up, see ya.
One final question before you go.
Oh, fine. What is it?
You said something that bothered
me, although I'm not sure you remember.
Yajima was just beaten to death!
There's no way you can call it off after
that! He would insist that we play on!
Yajima was killed with a sword.
We said so at the scene. Most people
would assume he had been slashed.
Not you. You used the word "beaten."
The murder weapon was rusty and never left it's sheath.
The murderer would have known that.
Just like you knew he was beaten to death.
That's because, I saw the body at the scene!
We're done!
Too bad the body was covered, just before you arrived.
There's no way you could've seen it... Not then.
So maybe I didn't..! Must have seen something else!
I guess I could tell from the way the blood
was spattered that he was beaten instead of cut!
Who cares? I told you that I
was innocent! Now leave me alone!
Now that we got him on the
ropes, I wonder what he's gonna do?
All we can do now is wait.
And focus on the contest hall.
Correct. I just checked on it.
There's gonna be trouble for sure.
Boy, it sure is massive huh...
Wait, what's that building on the side of the cliff?
It's called the Satsukido.
After his wife?
That's right. It's a tower Mr. Achiwa had
constructed in remembrance of his late wife.
It seems to go unused most of the year.
Says here that it's only used once
a year for the Satsuki Cup Finals.
Mr. Achiwa is the reader and only he
and the finalists are allowed inside.
Exactly, there's no live audience to witness the match.
They have a camera and microphones recording the whole
thing and then transmit it to an exclusive viewing hall.
That's actually kind of rad.
The temperature and humidity in the competition
hall, are kept stable by an HVAC system.
On top of that, the soundproof walls that surround
the building keep any outside noise from coming in.
It's all top of the line of course.
And build exclusively for Karuta... There's
nothing like it anywhere else in the world.
I'm getting hungry.
Let's go to the Buffet then!
I could really go for some cake!
The kids and I are gonna go hit the town. Alright?
Okay, have fun!
Mm!
We're ready to go Ran!
Time to head out and see the city!
We'll be back later tonight!
Bye!
We'll see you later!
Sorry, I'm ready to go!
Let's shop for souvenirs!
Oh, Mrs. Hattori! Let's get started!
Such enthusiasm.
But you're still not yet rested.
You must save some energy for the game.
But, I'm fine! Really!
No way, you've gotta be joking! You seriously
got a former queen to be your practice partner?
Sure did!
Awesome! You might actually stand a chance after all!
Heh! Let's hope! But the only
way to know is with more practice!
If you're looking to get some extra practice in, Hm?
I'd be more than happy to play a round with you?
But even with my help, I'm not sure
you'll be able to make it to the finals.
How dare you!
Huh?
Get some rest, Kazuha.
But I...
If you require practice, I'd be more than happy to oblige.
Wait, you're Shizuka Ikenami! Did
you come to help teach her Karuta?
No matter. I offer you my help as well.
If you insist Ms. Ikenami... It
would certainly be my pleasure.
Got any intel yet?
After this, the President and Mr. Sekine are going
to Achiwa Hall to rehearse for tomorrow's competition.
They've got a solid police escort,
so they should be fine from here on.
At least, until they're inside the hall, anyways.
What about Momiji?
Don't worry. Her house is in Kyoto,
so she's gonna head over with them.
Huh?
Just a sec.
I tracked down the ID of the man in that picture.
Definitely wasn't easy...
Really? Who is it?
Well, it might surprise you.
I just sent you the details.
Let me know if you got it.
Thanks! One more thing.
Hm?
What about the Karuta cards?
Just got them imported to the analysis software.
I should know which card he was holding in about an hour.
The system's compiling the data now.
That's great. Then give me a call
back as soon as the analysis is complete.
Right...
Bye Conan.
Huh...
Shikao Nagoro...
What the?
It's been a while since I've had so much fun. Thank you.
Let's go, Iori.
Right.
You know, you really do have some courage.
Huh?
Honestly, I'm impressed an amateur
would even think to play at this level.
It almost makes sense. My name means autumn leaf,
while Kazuha is a leaf in it's most simple form.
But.. But I...
That's quite enough young lady.
And I promise I won't be going easy on
you! That's a mistake I've made once before.
I took an amateur lightly, and
I underestimated their talents.
It was just awful. I was so embarrassed.
So that's why... I'm going to face
with you with everything I've got!
Ugh... Good! I want you to!
Please, I think that's enough Karuta talk for one day.
In any case, are you sure it's okay that you're here?
The President must be worried about you.
Your concern is touching...
But I am fine exactly where I am.
Honestly, I feel safe anywhere.
Now that I know Heiji Hattori will be watching over me.
Just what do you mean by that?!
Goodness, of course, I imagine you wouldn't know.
Heiji's become my new private bodyguard.
What?!
He was keeping watch at my house all evening. I'd
wager the poor dear didn't even get a wink of sleep!
I simply cannot wait for the contest tomorrow.
Best of luck to you little Miss Leaf.
Heiji, I must have underestimated you!
Hey, it's okay! You're way stronger than she is!
Heiji!
I don't know what kind of relationship
you think you have with this girl,
but she's dead meat in this Karuta contest!
Do you hear me? Dead meat!!
Well said indeed.
What is it?
I don't know, but I just felt a
chill shoot straight down my spine!
Um... Did you catch a cold or something?
No, it's way worse than that.
Like something demonic..!
Oh...
Huh?
Oh..!
Hey, here they come.
President Achiwa.
Momiji Ooka.
And Sekine.
They're all here.
Woah!
Aah!!
Ugh... Another explosion?!
That was Sekine's car!
All right, how's Mr. Sekine doing?
The last we heard from the hospital,
he still hasn't regained consciousness.
His chance of recovery is 50-50.
And Miss Ooka was also caught in the
explosion. Was she brought to the hospital as well?
It seems she wasn't hurt.
But she and her driver went to the hospital
to get checked out. Just to be on the safe side.
We've had two bombing attacks in as many days.
Frankly, Mr. Achiwa, I think it's
time you fill us in. Wouldn't you agree?
Huh?
The evidence all leads to one conclusion.
The bombing at Nichiuri was likely an
attempt to target the Satsuki Association.
Hmm...
Excuse me, sir.
Hm?
Do you recognize the man in this photograph?
H-How did you get your hands on that picture?
That hardly matters. It's time to stop hiding things.
We've given you the benefit of the doubt, but this
is the moment for you to come clean. Let's hear it.
I guess it is... Some time ago,
there was a Karuta Club in Kyoto.
A small group of 20 or so
exceptionally talented players...
They would gather each month to learn and train.
And the one leading that club,
was a master named Shikao Nagoro.
He was quite skilled.
Many assumed it was only a matter of
time before he became a champion himself.
The problem was that he was solely fixated on winning.
His style of Karuta was not exactly
what any player would call refined.
Son of a... Hey!
Give me that card! I was faster, damn it!
Why the hell was I penalized! What are you, blind?!
It was five years ago...
Nagoro... He wanted to play in a competition,
just so he could go up against my late wife.
The condition was the losing side would close their club.
Seriously? All this over a card game?
But Satsuki certainly wasn't obligated
to accept the challenge, was she?
Mr. Nagoro went straight to the media...
He made a number of statements that would
have made it difficult for Satsuki to refuse.
He said our Association would
avoid the challenge out of fear...
So what you're telling us is that, your wife
accepted this challenge under duress, is that right?
Then what? I assum Satsuki was the victor?
It was never meant to come to pass, I'm afraid.
Huh?
Everything was set up, but
Mr. Nagoro himself never arrived.
As a result, Satsuki was declared the victor by default.
In the end, Nagoro was labeled as a coward
who brought shame to the world of Karuta.
Even though he was the one who
started this whole media circus...
He vanished, never to be seen again.
Interesting, if he disappeared what
happened to the rest of the Nagoro club?
Once their President disappeared, their club disbanded.
Without a force to lead them,
most of their players scattered.
All right sir, come clean with us. All of this
is based on some grudge against your association?
It's possible.
Back when this rivalry began, the most
outspoken proponent of closing the Nagoro Club...
Was the recently deceased Mr. Yajima...
Huh?
Excuse me?
The Satsuki Association wanted to settle
things peacefully without a big fuss.
But it seems little was meant to go our way.
So then, what happened ot the members of the Nagoro Club?
After all they'd been through, we were glad
to offer them membership to our organization.
However, only two chose to accept.
And let me guess just who those two are...
Yes... Momiji Ooka and Mr. Sekine.
The very same ones caught up in the bombing incident?
Yes. Each were devoted to him.
Momiji Ooka was Nagoro's most
dedicated student. She was his protege.
In fact, Momiji and her master
both favor the exact same cards.
When one with a maple leaf appears
on the board, they would never miss.
She and Sekine were without a doubt,
Nagoro's fiercest disciples.
Why do you think Nagoro's students
are so well trained with the maple cards?
I hear it's because Nagoro's first name is Shikao.
As in, deer meat?
Exactly. "Momiji" is another
word that shares that meaning.
I'm sure Nagoro can't have been very
happy about losing his most promising student.
Especially not to his rivals in the Satsuki Association.
So the question is, why seek revenge now?
And more to the point. Why would he then
want to warn his targets about the bombing?
This is just speculation...
But if he's been radio silent for five years now,
maybe that was less of a warning and more an
announcement of his return to the spotlight.
If that's the case...
we should proceed
under the assumption,
that this is Nagoro's attempt to
take revenge on the Satsuki Association.
Hm?
Huh? Excuse me.
What is it?
Yes. We should establish a joint
investigation headquarters with the Kyoto Police.
Right.
What?!
Huh?
Chief Inspector! Headquarters checked Mr. Sekine's phone.
He got a strange email just moments before the explosion!
Well what did it say?
It looks like the sender was anonymous. - Huh?
But there was an image of a
Karuta card attached to the email!
And what was the poem on that card?
Ah! "Since I could bring no
offering, behold mount Tamuke..."
"Here are brocades of maple
leaves, as a tribute to the gods..."
That's one of Nagoro's cards!
Huh?
What are you thinking, Heiji?
Just give me a second.
I think Momiji's in danger.
Mr. Iori?
Is this Mr. Hattori?
Listen, I need you to check Momiji's emails.
See if there's anything from
an unknown address. And hurry!
Emails?
What's wrong, Iori?
It's a call from young Mr. Hattori.
Heiji is calling? Here let me see!
Momiji! I need you to check your emails for me, okay?
My emails? What's going on?
You know, I was starting to think
you'd never call but I'm so glad you did!
Uuh...
Haha...
Hey... That's odd?
Huh?
There's an attachment.
A Karuta card?
Wow! How'd you know that Heiji?
I need you to read me the poem.
Ah- hm...
"From Mimuro's mountain slopes, maple leaves are torn..."
The Maple leaves..! Momiji, I need you to listen.
you cannot go back home tonight!
Come straight to the Osaka Police Department!
You hear me?
I can't do that, my dear. Not even for you.
Huh?!
The Satsuki Cup is tomorrow, and I must prepare.
Momiji, I don't think you
understand! Your life may be in danger!
Nothing bad will happen to
me. After all Heiji, I have you!
Ugh..!
You're going to protect me.
I know you will.
Huh?
I haven't forgotten the promise we made.
What promise?
Bye now!
Wha-!
Damn it! She hung up on me!
In any case, if she received one
of those threats we need her secure.
Hmm...
Then let's move. I want a full
security detail on Miss Ooka immediately!
Yes, sir!
Hmm... It would appear Mr. Yajima is
the only one that a card wasn't sent to...
That actually isn't the truth. There was a
threat card found where Yajima was murdered.
It would appear, that Nagoro is
the actual murderer of Mr. Yajima.
Before he left the scene, he
left his favorite card on the body.
Sekine saw the card when he arrived later,
and attempted to conceal Nagoro's involvement.
So what you're saying is he
knew that Nagoro was the killer...
And moreover, the presence of
that Karuta card would implicate him.
So Sekine staged a robbery, and ransacked the house.
All to cover up the crime his former master had committed.
Hold on...
Are you suggesting Sekine was at the
crime scene even before the police arrived?
Yes, it's the only thing that ties the theories together.
As to evidence...
We called in an expert.
Using the direction and pattern of the
blood stains, on the cards and the carpet...
Good.
She has determined precisely how the
cards were lined up at the time of the murder.
Take a look at the screen.
The cards on the right were already on the
floor. So they have Mr. Yajima's blood on them.
As for the cards on the left...
Some were clean and others were smeared with
blood as the killer attempted to mix them in.
And some are slightly bent. Judging by
that as well as the other bloodstains...
The card in Mr. Yajima's hand was...
Number 32!
That's a Harumichi!
"High in a mountain stream, there
is a barrier built by the wind..."
"Yet it is only maple leaves that cannot escape..."
Okay, so one of Nagoro's favorite
cards was found at the crime scene too!
Look at this. These are the
cards that accompanied each crime.
From the upper left, found at Nichiuri TV.
Yajima's residence.
Sekine's email.
And the one Momiji just found.
Only a single word, "Momiji" appears in all four cards.
Good work. They're all part of the
cards Nagoro has a preference for.
Hmm... So our killer, either shares
that proclivity, or must be Shikao Nagoro.
I didn't want to believe Nagoro would be
capable of such things, but it must be him.
What worries me is there are 6 maple
cards Nagoro always used to win...
So we better keep our eyes open.
What do you mean by that?
He means there are still two cards left.
If Nagoro is using his favorite Karuta Poems
as a calling card before every single attack,
then I have no doubt in my mind
he's got a plan ready for the last two.
There may be more after Miss Ooka?
I'm certain that he's got 2
more victims waiting in the wings.
Time's a factor.
Nagoro has already begun to exact his revenge.
Well done! You boys are truly incredible. I'm
certain you'll bring this murderer to justice!
Mm. But in order to do that,
we're gonna need more information.
So just what happened between you and Mr. Nagoro?
I... I already...
Something happened.
Do you want to help us or not?
I do but...
Fine... I couldn't say before, but I trust you.
Come by my hotel this evening.
... and I'll fill you both in on
what exactly happened five years ago.
Okay, you guys wait here!
I'll run this inside to Momiji.
Okay!
Not a problem!
Sounds good!
Ma'am. The police called just a moment ago.
They wanted your permission to
increase security around the house.
Then I will trust their judgement.
Excuse me?
Huh?
I'm glad to hear you're okay. I
stopped by to drop off your wallet!
Ah! I'm so glad you came!
I'm in your debt! Truly, thank you so much!
It's okay!
Here you go. Really I'm just happy to help.
Ah! So sweet! The lucky charm in here means so much to me.
I wasn't sure I'd do well in the competition
without it. But now I'm certain I'll win!
Though I suppose I shouldn't have mentioned that.
I certainly don't want you to feel
as though you're aiding the enemy.
Uh- no!
I do hope your friend doesn't hurt
her fingers from practicing too hard.
Such pretty nails!
The manicure is more about keeping
them protected than anything else.
You have to make sure they're cared for to play well.
So I do my best to keep them like this.
Well, they're beautiful!
Oh and...
I had to look inside your case
for your contact info, so...
Ah...
I may have seen something...
Ah! I'm going to bet you mean this photograph, don't you?
Because it kind of looks like...
It's little Heiji!
Thought so...
It's from a Karuta contest I
entered when I was just a child.
It was Heiji who beat me in the final round.
I was crying... When Heiji saw he walked over and said...
Hey, don't cry.
Because the next time we meet,
I'm going to take you for my bride.
Uh... Really?
Really.
I promise.
Huh?!
He proposed to her?!
And that's the moment sweet Heiji became my husband to be.
But you can't be serious, you were only little kids!
A promise is still a promise.
Uuh...
When a man says something like that, they shouldn't
be able to just change their minds the next day.
Ah...
I wish I could Ran, but I can't
read the mind of a girl I really like!
I guess you're right...
"A swift stream..."
"Though it becomes divided by a boulder...
Will one day join together again..."
Huh...
I've always believed.
Even though Heiji and I were so
far apart, our hearts were still one.
Tell Miss Leaf something for me.
Uh... Miss Leaf?
I was taught... When I choose a Karuta card to go after...
Never let anyone take it from me.
Momiji...
Ran?
Ran!
Huh?!
Yeah?
What is going on with you?
You've been acting weird ever since
you came back from looking around the city.
Sorry.
How are you feeling, Kazuha?
Huh? Okay, I guess...
Heiji's mother told me that if I want a real chance at
winning the competition. I have to pick a favorite card.
But there are so many... It's hard to decide.
I think you're over complicating it.
Huh?
The Hyakunin-Isshu's full of love poems.
So why don't you stop thinking about winning,
and pick a poem that really speaks to you?
That speaks to me...
For me... I would pick this one!
Oh, that's Meeting on the Path! By Murasaki Shikibu.
It's about friends who have to part
ways only a little while after they meet.
Mhm, yeah. The minute I see
Shinichi, he runs off somewhere.
And there's so much I want to say to him.
That's true. I guess, for me...
Maybe..
“I promised myself..."
"No one would ever know of my love for you."
"But in the end, my face gave me away..."
I think it describes your feelings perfectly.
That's a great pick, Kazuha.
Even Momiji saw how much you care for him.
Not that she thinks I'm gonna
be much of a challenge anyway.
Urk...
She acts like they're already engaged.
You saw how she's all over him!
I guess so...
Of course she's all over him.
She thinks they're already engaged.
Can't let Kazuha know that though.
What?
So Nagoro and Satsuki had another match, the
night before they were actually supposed to compete?
That's right. He came by when I was out.
That article says he disappeared because he
was scared of actually competing against Satsuki.
... But he arrived the night
before, so that can't be the truth.
And do you have any idea why?
I don't... And unless we can find a way to
ask him, I suppose we'll never really know.
My wife believed he wanted to use our Association's
cards to defeat her, thus adding insult to injury.
Was that the deck they used?
I thought those cards were being kept in a museum
when they weren't being used for the Satsuki Cup?
At that time, no one had ever attempted
to steal them. So we just kept them at home.
How could they have had a match
without someone to read off the poetry?
Well, you see all those cassettes in the cabinet there?
That's how even the best used to
practice Karuta back in the old days.
And then? How did the match turn out?
Satsuki beat him out right. - Hm...
Seems line Nagoro never stood a chance against her.
I was coming back home just as they finished the match.
As soon as I opened the door, I remember
Nagoro went pale and fled in a panic.
Neither I, nor anyone else, has seen him since that day.
After he disappeared, why didn't
you tell the police any of this?
Honestly, I was worried it might leak
to the media and the other club members.
The rest of them would have been far from happy if
they'd known we used those cards for a private match.
I thought it best to keep the whole thing quiet, frankly.
Not what I would have done, but fair enough I suppose...
It's not that I don't trust the police but...
Huh?
You detectives always seem at least a step ahead.
Something's wrong with this picture.
Is it just that Achiwa had a different car back then?
The two of you must capture Nagoro before it's too late.
Yeah, we'll close this case.
Two cubes isn't gonna do it.
Huh?
I'm gonna need two more...
My brain is craving something sweet.
Uuh... Mhm!
She heard that?
Hmph.This girl...
I'm no good at using "Kakoite" or "Watarite" yet.
And I can't find a rhythm...
If I can't get better...
She's gonna take Heiji away from me, I know it!
Hey, Kazuha!
Huh?
Looks like you're out for blood.
Aah! Heiji!
All geared up for a fight, huh?
Why don't you just shut up?
Aren't you supposed to be watching over
Momiji? Why don't you run on back then?
What is up with you?
I came all the way back here to give my old
lady a break, so why are you being so mean to me?
I used to beat you all the time!
Oh, I'm way better than I was in grade
school! I'd wipe the floor with you.
Hey, I was wondering...
Do you remember anything strange about the
Karuta contest you entered when you were a kid?
Like specifically, about the girl in the finals?
Actually, I think I do! That's it!
I was winning left and right!
Hold on a sec, did you remember something after all?
Yeah, I won in the finals over some girl
and she just starting crying like crazy!
I think that girl was Momiji!
Wait, really?!
Anything else that comes to mind?
Huh?
Don't think so?
Like maybe making a promise to little Momiji or something?
I think I might have said, "Better
luck next time!" or something...
Doesn't matter. Just got back to her.
Hm?
You're supposed to be her bodyguard right?
I'm pretty sure the police are gonna...
Just go, okay?
If she gets hurt before the
contest, then I won't be able to win.
Fine. I guess I'll go then...
Mom.
Good luck with training.
Hm.
Uuh...
"I promised myself..."
"No one would ever know of my love for you..."
"But in the end, my face gave me away..."
"And people asked me, 'what's wrong?'"
Master Nagoro.
Please guide me in this competition,
as you have always done before.
My most precious Satsuki...
Watch over us...
"These plum blossoms in Naniwazu..."
"Once sheltered in winter..."
"But now that spring crosses the land..."
"At long last they have bloomed..."
"These plum blossoms... At long last they have bloomed..."
Hm...
"From Mount Yoshino..."
She did it! She got the card!
Good think she wore that
uniform! It makes her easy to spot!
Uh-huh!
Isn't that an Aikido uniform?
Something just came up. He had to go help out Heiji!
Otherwise he'd be here for sure!
Hey, you guys!
Why don't send Conan that picture we
took, of Genta at the souvenir shop?
Hmm...
They were so mad!
Sounds like it started.
Guess so.
With security as tight as it is now,
there's no chance Nagoro can get in.
That's right. We're ready for him.
No one will be able to make it through the gate.
Unless they registered as staff beforehand.
We did thorough background checks.
We took every possible measure.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Uh, it's probably nothing...
Huh?
What's this?
Oh, it's from Mitsuhiko.
What's Genta doing? Grabbing
food like that with his bare hands..
I see.
"As the dew..."
"Promises the thirsty..."
Momiji... She's the first to move up.
Did Kazuha win yet?
No, not yet.
Hey! Look that's her!
It is! It's Kazuha!
Aw yeah!
Keep on going Kazuha!
She got through the first round. Not a bad start at all.
Mr. Sekine! Are you alright?
Thank you for the match.
Who would have thought she'd make it to the finals?
I'm just surprised to find a
player with that much raw talent.
Hooray!
You think she'll win?
No question!
It's really happening! She's on her way to victory!
She's so caught up in the moment...
I wonder if she's thinking of what
she'll say to Heiji if she wins...
So she's still in! That's great to see.
Looks like she's up against Momiji in the finals.
That's right.
What?!
Huh?
You're telling me, Mr. Sekine is awake again?
Uh-huh... Yes I understand.
I'll leave security here to the
Kyoto Police and be there soon.
Sekine regained consciousness?
Yeah that's right, and it turns out
Heiji's prediction was right on the money.
I still don't see why Sekine went to Yajima's...
Sounds like Yajima had been asking a
lot of questions about Nagoro recently.
Sekine found out...
I suppose he thought if he kept a close eye on
Yajima, he might be able to track down his former mentor.
So you think Sekine realized something had
gone wrong and stormed in only to find the body?
It's likely...
I'll be sure to get all the details from
Mr. Sekine as soon as I'm back in Osaka.
All right. Kyoto will handle things while you're gone.
Good.
Hey, hold on. I'll go with you!
Hmm... This is the last one.
Can't imagine why he wants it
here but... At least it's over with.
Huh?!
Is there a fire?
If there was, the alarms would be going off...
Think it's another bomb?
There's no way. You've got to be kidding!
What's going on out there?
Hey, what's out in the west forrest?
Oh uh, nothing but an old storeroom I think, sir.
Are there any security cameras?
Nothing outside the facility is covered.
Damn it all...
You think it's another explosion?
It is... Come on!
That's the Satsukido. We'll be there shortly.
Wow...
There's a smell in the air...
Ah...
We've just had the elevator refitted.
Some of the lubricant smell must still
linger... I'm sorry, does it bother you?
No, it's fine. I was just
curious. This is all so new to me.
I'm incredibly excited and, I'm
sure I can't be the only one...
To tell the truth, I never thought I'd get
this far, and my heart's beating out of my chest...
But I'm sure you're used to all this...
I promise my heart is beating just as hard as yours.
Huh?
I'm in love with Heiji. I can't wait to tell him
everything I feel, but I don't know what he'll say.
I won't lose... I can't lose...
You don't want to get any closer than this.
What's going on?
Inspector!
Oh.
Another bomb?
Yes, sir. One victim...
The body's in bad shape...
We won't be able to identify it
until we get back to the morgue.
So the bomb was set here...
The question is exactly how, and when?
Based on early evidence, we think it's
possible the victim brought the bomb in himself, sir
He what?
Nagoro accidentally blew himself up?
Sir!
Hm?
Yes, this is Inspector Ayanokoji.
Ah...
What's wrong?
Hattori, take a look at that.
What is it? A ring?
Probably the victim's.
There you are. What have you found?
Take a look a the ring in this
tree. We think it may be the victim's.
It's rather bulky...
Yeah, they're not usually so big.
A big ring? Wait...
... It's Kaieda!
Huh? Wait, you mean Achiwa's secretary? Togo Kaieda?
Yeah, I'm positive! In pictures, he
was always wearing it on his thumb!
If that's his ring, is Kaieda our murderer?
No...
No, because If we hadn't found this ring, then we would
be absolutely sure that the body over there is Nagoro's!
Now I see... This bomb was supposed to
make it look like Mr. Nagoro had died.
Huh?
Hold on...
If the real murderer wanted to
make it look like Nagoro was dead...
Then what about the other two maple leaf cards?
They've probably already been sent out to the targets!
We already know one.
I got another call from Inspector Otaki.
And he told me that he had Mr. Achiwa's
secretary go over his emails again.
A Karuta card had arrived in the mail this morning.
Which means there's only one card left.
Ugh...
One card left...
And only the finals to play.
That's it!
Huh?
If Mr. Achiwa already received
his card, there's only one card left.
The only reason there would still be one
card is if he hadn't decided who to send it to!
Oh no, Inspector! Get someone to
check Kazuha Toyama's phone, hurry!
Huh? Yeah! But tell me what's going on?
That's why there's only one card not accounted for!
The killer held onto it because he didn't
know who was gonna make it to the finals!
You're saying...
His targets..!
Are the finalists in the Satsukido!
I am sorry that it had to be you.
Huh?
I know there is such pressure in a match of this
caliber, but play to the best of your abilities.
We'll do our very best.
Ready, set... Go Kazuha!
Time to show them just how skilled you are.
What have you got?
Did you find the card?
Yes, she just got it. About 15 minutes ago.
A poem was sent to Kazuha.
Tell them to cancel the finals right now! Get moving!
Come on, Kudo!
Where are you going?
We'll take the bike!
What? Sir, you want me to cancel the finals?
Yes, sir. Right away!
One moment, I'll give them a call!
Huh?
Just an earthquake. I'm certain
it's not big enough to worry about.
Let's...
Hey, why'd it cut out?
Do you think maybe it's broken?
Oh, come on.
It's a black out?
No, the lights are on.
Hurry! It's started!
Yeah! Hang on tight!
How are we gonna get to the Satsukido?!
Just trust me! I've got an idea.
That's never good!
I've never seen that water gleam...
Thought so...
Miss Leaf didn't even try...
She won't bother going for the cards I'm good at.
In this dire distress...
Damn, that's no ordinary fire.
There must be some kind of
accelerant fueling the fire, Inspector.
Have the Firefighters arrived yet?
The roads in the garden are so narrow that
there's now way for the engines to get through...
It's only a matter of time
before the tower goes up in flames!
Yes, sir.
Then the game is up...
Hey, do you still think that Nagoro is the killer?
No, only one person could have
re-registered Kaieda as staff!
Even though he quit the association!
Only one person could have given him the bomb..!
President Kensuke Achiwa!
I think he's planning to blow himself
up and take the two girls with him!
Not if I have anything to say about it!
The card's in a tough to reach spot...
And Momiji knows it's the poem I love...
No way is she gonna make this easy...
Hmph. She's going after this card for sure.
Well, she can't have it. My card, my win.
I have to get it... I have to! No matter what it takes.
Quiet, quiet, quiet!
Get this stupid pounding out of my head!
Hey, Kazuha!
Looks like you're out for blood.
All geared up for a fight, huh?
A moment, please.
Hm.
I'm not supposed to fight. It won't help.
The hum of the air conditioner,
the rustling of my kimono...
The soft tap upon the cards...
The beat of my heart...
These sounds that fill my mind. All of
them are a part of me. They make me who I am.
Thank you, sir.
I will find the real sound!
Of the pine trees growing there, I come back to you...
We were supposed to believe all these crimes,
were Nagoro's attempt to take
revenge on the Satsuki Association.
That's what Achiwa wanted us to think!
Nagoro and Satsuki were set to play
a match over the fate of their clubs.
But instead Nagoro showed up the
night before and they played then!
Achiwa told us that Satsuki won that match...
But there's something that's been bothering me about it.
It was the picture in the article wasn't it?
Yeah. The article said Mr. Achiwa always washes his
car, before one of Satsuki's games for good luck...
But the car was dirty!
He didn't have to take the time to wash it as usual.
Because he knew Nagoro wouldn't show!
Cold and unpitying was my love...
Nice try, but I know I was faster this time.
No, you may have been close, but I was faster!
In fact, I think you'd know
that better than anybody! Hands off.
Hm...
When this competition began I never
imagined this is how it would play out...
But if Satsuki actually lost
that match from five years ago,
that sounds like motive to me!
Me too! To protect the honor
of the club, he silenced Nagoro!
When Yajima saw footage of the
contest, he must have realized,
what had really happened, and what Mr. Achiwa had done!
So what evidence was hidden in those Karuta cards!?
If Mr. Achiwa grabbed the cards after they
had been splattered with Nagoro's blood...
There'd be fingerprints!
I didn't realize until Mitsuhiko sent me that picture!
But I'm pretty sure that
Mr.Achiwa's prints are on those cards.
That's why Yajima wanted to do a
Karuta broadcast with the Association!
... so footage of the cards they
played with could be used as evidence!
It's also why the bombing and Yajima's
murder occurred at approximately the same time.
Of course!
There's one other thing bothering me though!
Why bring the crime to his own
hall, or the finals for that matter?!
What if Nagoro's body is buried at
Satsukido? What if it has always been there?
That really would be the perfect place, wouldn't it?
Achiwa had this whole thing
planned out from the beginning!
Even if he managed to pull of the
perfect crime and frame Mr. Nagoro...
It would all be for naught if
the body was discovered later!
Ah, there it is!
Yeah!
I dislike nothing so much as the breaking light of day...
The depths of the hearts...
A fake!
The fire's so high up already!
Not good!
We've gotta put it out... But what can we do?!
That's on you Kudo! I need you to
figure out how to extinguish the fire!
What are you doing?! Wait!!
Here we go!
Go!
What's going on?!
Hup!
Come on, just a little more!
There isn't much time! I gotta hurry!
The whole tower's on fire!
Stay right where you are!
Heiji?!
What the heck are you doing here?!
The waterfall's changed direction!
It's a miracle!
It's almost out!
What the hell is going on up there?
Looks like I made it just in the nick of time.
Nice work there, Kudo.
Heiji! How did you manage to get up here?!
You both should go back inside, it's dangerous.
Wait, Conan?! What is going on?
How'd you even get here?
Well, maybe you're better to
answer one of those, Mr. Achiwa.
What are you talking about?
Get behind me and stay back.
What? Heiji, tell me what's going on...
I found the cards, but I bet you
don't want me looking at them do you?
Just hold on! What is he talking about, Heiji?
Mr. Achiwa here is the only one who
can finally put this case to rest...
Huh?!
One year ago. That's when it all
started. When Momiji won the match here.
You'd seen those tactics in play only once before,
and her stack of victory cards
looked at lot like those that
Mr. Nagoro had taken during his match with your late wife.
Master Nagoro did more than teach me offensive Karuta...
He taught me his favorite cards!
But even so... What you're
suggesting is almost impossible.
Almost, doesn't make it impossible.
There are black smears on the side
of the Associations prized cards.
And it just so happens that Mister Yajima, one of
the murder victims, was the first person to notice.
What could be so important about that stain?
Because in that stain is the fingerprint of whoever
grabbed the card with Nagoro's blood spattered on it.
That mark is Master Nagoro's blood?!
It was believed Nagoro disappeared five
years ago, but in truth he was actually murdered.
... No...
And that fingerprint could only have come from...
Mr. Nagoro's killer.
Hmph... Excellent reasoning
boys. I supposed I should confess.
But in return, I ask only that you not
submit the Association's cards as evidence.
Please... The cards.
So that's the true end to the story.
Huh?
There was one thing I didn't understand.
But now it makes sense.
The fingerprints on these cards
aren't yours, are they, Mr. Achiwa?
No, they are... I'll swear to it. They're mine.
That's right.
Huh?
This time, you and Mr. Kaieda were
behind everything that's happened.
But Mr. Nagoro's murder five years
ago was someone else... wasn't it?
Satsuki was the killer.
Hmm...
As soon as I saw my Satsuki... I knew what she'd done.
Nagoro challenged her to a match, and she lost.
They'd played the old way, using
one of my cassettes as the reader.
It was the shame that forced her hand...
Satsuki had practiced with those
cassettes nearly every day for so many years.
There were dozens of possible patterns of cards and poems,
But still, she had a talent, and
practically knew each of them all by heart.
She started this game with a grand advantage, and yet..!
Nagoro was able to defeat her so easily.
He was so much more gifted
than we ever could have believed.
I can only imagine the fear she felt in that moment...
She must have thought of the humilitation
she knew she would have to face the next day.
So she took his life, because my Satsuki
could never have born the weight of that loss...
Where once she was beautiful and radiant, she grew hollow.
She abandoned her duties to the
Association... She fell ill and...
Two years after that day, she died...
This is the truth.
I hope that you can understand...
Huh?!
Don't!
Stop this!
This is all Nagoro's fault.
If he hadn't humiliated her that day,
then none of this would have ever come to pass.
That wasn't what he wanted...
Huh?
I know the real reason he went to
challenge Satsuki the day before...
Ah...
I asked him about the rivalry a long time ago...
I needed to know why he held such a
strong grudge against Satsuki's Karuta Club.
A grudge? I suppose that's how it looks from the outside.
This is the only way I'll have a
chance to truly play against her...
To win so that she might acknowledge
what a capable player I've become.
To hear praise from my first love.
His... first love?
That's right.
The only reason he started playing to begin
with was because of his admiration for Satsuki.
Then, he discovered he was sick.
That in a year his vision would be gone completely, and...
I think that's why he started
playing as aggressively as he did...
He was so sure he didn't have much time left.
So Nagoro only wanted to impress her the night before.
He'd always planned to let her win the actual game.
Master Nagoro wanted a reason for the
Satsuki Association to care for his students.
He knew in the end he wouldn't
be able to care for them himself.
The truth is Satsuki had no idea...
So she ended up killing Mr. Nagoro.
Please no...
... Satsuki.
What have I done?
Wh-What's happening?!
Kazuha!
Woah!
Ugh...
Are you okay?!
Yeah!
I don't know if I can stand..!
Hurry up! Get on the elevator!
Momiji! Come on!
O-Okay!
All right, we gotta get out of here.
I'm staying here. Please go without me...
I won't leave you!
Huh?
I'm not just gonna let you die!
Momiji!
Huh?
You have to climb on!
A-All right..!
Kazuha!
Huh?
Climb up here!
Hurry! Ugh!
Almost!
I gotcha!
Huh?!
No! No..!
Come on..!
Stay up just a little longer!
Woah! Ah!
Aah!!
Haah!! Gah!
Woah!
Gah!
Ah!
Hang on! I'll be right there!
That was too close for comfort...
Hattori!!
It's all coming down! We gotta go! Get out of here!
Ugh... Mm...
Huh?! No, wait!
Don't just leave us here!
Huh..? Heiji!
Hurry, get on!
This one's alright.
Hattori... Kazuha...
You've gotta get out of there!
Heiji, look!
Yeah, I know.
Hm...
Heiji, what are you doing?
I'm gonna need you to hang on tight!
You are not planning to jump
across that gap! You are not!!
I sure as hell am!
Ah! No way!
Look how far that is! We'll never make it!
Listen to me!
Let's just jump for the lake! That's safer right?
You can't!
If we hit it from this altitude,
the water would be like concrete.
Now hang on tight, Kazuha!
I won't let you die here!
We got one shot!
We're not gonna die!
Not here, and not today!!
Wait... is that them?!
There's something I have to tell you!
I've been waiting a long time!
A motorcycle...?!
Here we go!!!
Heiji!
Kazuha!
Kazuha.
You okay?
Yeah.
I think we've cheated death enough times for one week.
Hmph, those two are something else.
Honestly, I wasn't sure we were gonna make it.
And if we didn't?
Huh?
What was it that you wanted to say to me?
Uuh! I dunno what you're talking about..!
When we were in the air. You said
you had something you needed to tell me.
Maybe you were hearing things.
No way! My hearnings pretty sharp
after all that Karuta training.
Come on! What is it Heiji, tell me!
Hey wait a- woah!
Tell me what it is!
Look, I said wait a second!
You said you had something to say Hattori, so say it!
I-It's not like it...!
Thanks for coming out to see us off!
Really, we're the ones who should be thanking you!
By the way, what ever happened to your Karuta Club?
Oh yeah! The school was so impressed
that we made it all the way to the finals,
turns out we don't have to shut down after all!
Thought I still can't believe
I lost in the very last round...
Kazuha... Uh.
Come here.
Huh?
What's that about?
I dunno, must be some kind of secret.
Really?
Yeah, but it's okay. I got the card I really wanted!
I'm so glad you chose a poem that really spoke to you.
Not quite. It wasn't just the poem.
It was the name of it's author too!
Taira-no-Kanemori.
And it just so happens,
his name begins with the same
exact character as Heiji's does!
So in my eyes, that card read simply as Heiji's name!
I think I wanna send a picture of the poem to Heiji later.
I wanna telll him that's how I really feel...
You're going to send him a poem?
Perhaps confess your love?
Isn't that against the rules?
Momiji?
Did you hear all of that?
You aren't the only one with good ears, you know?
Hey, Momiji!
I didn't think we'd run into you here.
I came to confess to you my deepest feelings.
Though I remember well, that beautiful
day you told me the truth of your own.
Huh? What do you mean?
This picture is all the proof I need.
They're pinky swearing!
That's pretty solid evidence...
If you break a pinky swear you have to swallow needles.
Hold on just a sec! What kind of promise did I make you?
That next time that we met, you'd
take me as your bride, of course?
Huh?!
Why do his embarrassing moments always get recorded...
It's old, but this picture is
proof of the promise you swore to me.
Oh, I remember now. That makes way more sense!
What I actually said was,
"Don't cry, you've just gotta practice some more! If
you don't, next time I'm gonna take you for a ride!”
Uh...
Really..?
That's what you said?
I was going easy on her, I just
wanted her to know next time I wouldn't.
Heh... It was probably stupid...
Iori, we're leaving.
Of course, ma'am.
Fine. I shall let you go this day.
But keep in mind. I never give
up a card once it's in my sights.
Don't you ever forget that.
Kazuha.
Huh?
Hmph!
Wait, does that mean you're looking for a rematch, Momiji?
Hey, Sonoko?
You know a lot about the Hyakunin-Isshu, isn't that right?
Yeah, my family plays Karuta every New Year's!
I sent Shinichi a picture of
the card "Meeting on the path.
He sent back a poem about a stream divided.
It was beautiful but I totally forgot what it means.
"Even though in this moment I am
separated from the one who has my heart..."
"One day, I know, that we will meet again."
It's a love poem that Emperor Sutoku.
How sweet!
H-Hold on! Sonoko!
And you better remember that...
Zero.