[SAKURA yells]
[SAKURA] Ow!
Heh. I like those
screams diva. Keep it up.
[SAKURA whimpers]
[SAKURA]
This is pathetic.
I can't fight back.
I can't do anything.
[KAZAMA] Let's see
how you like this one!
That feel good?
[SAKURA] Ah! No!
That hurts even worse!
Aaahhhh!
Well, if it hurts so bad,
why don't you tap out already?
[SAKURA] I didn't
know it at the time,
but that was the beginning
of everything for me.
[MC (F)] It's time for the Sweet
Diva Center Vocal Fan Election!
Where just one vote
could change everything!
Only one pop idol
can take center stage!
Will it be Sakura Hagiwara?
Or, will Elena Miyazawa snatch
victory from the jaws of defeat?
[SAKURA] Wow, Elena,
you're going all out!
[ELENA] Show me your worst,
Sakura, I'm not losing this one!
Time for the grand finale!
All right!
Let's give 'em something
to really scream about!
[Pop song plays
indistinctly]
[ELENA and SAKURA]
It's the Ice Cream Sault!
[CROWD cheers]
Thanks guys,
you're the best!
[MC (F)] The votes are in!
We have a winner!
It was a close call, but only
one girl can claim the crown!
The fourth Sweet Diva Center
Vocal election goes to...
...Sakura Hagiwara!
[SAKURA gasps]
[CROWD cheers]
Yay!
[MC (F)] The fans have spoken!
Sakura is their queen
and they want more!
That's four in a row
for the reigning champ!
Better luck next time, Elena!
You were only one hundred and
twenty votes away from victory!
[ELENA] Sakura.
Congrats on the win,
but I'm taking
your spot next time.
[SAKURA]
Bring it on, partner.
[SAKURA hums]
[YUHO and AIKA]
Sakura! Congratulations!
Thanks, Yuho, thanks Aika.
It was close.
So tell me the secret
to victory, your majesty!
Forget that, what's the
secret to that hot body?
I don't know if that's--
Wow, is that muscle
I feel under there?
[YUHO]
Boob muscle isn't a thing.
Why can't I have
a figure like that?
If you want to be like
Sakura that badly,
you can start by
training harder.
She doesn't like to
let her fans down,
so she keeps herself in
tip-top shape all the time.
All for the fans?
Oh, Nanami.
Not to mention, she has a tough
rival to keep her on her toes.
Right?
[YUHO and AIKA] Elena!
Can you teach us
how to be awesome?
[ELENA] Yeah.
Lesson one is "stop grabbing
people's boobs," okay?
[MAKOTO] All right, ladies,
nice work out there!
The Fan Election was
a massive success.
We picked up a ton of new work!
I'm getting exhausted
just looking at it.
You beast!
You're such a slave driver!
So we've resorted
to name-calling, huh?
Then maybe I should
show you how much
of a slave driver
I can really be.
[MAKOTO chuckles]
Girl's Professional wrestling?
Yep! A one-day tryout
for a TV special.
What?
And how exactly is
this a job for an idol?
Look, if it's popular,
we need a hand in it,
and right now,
wrestling is big.
I guess, but that's
too scary for me!
Well, it's not like the
entire group has to go.
Though I'd be grateful
for some volunteers.
If no one else wants to go,
I think I can handle it.
[MAKOTO] I'm sure you could
Sakura, but you're our star.
Are you sure you want
to spend your time--
[ELENA]
I want to go with her!
Elena?
Now this is rare!
And here I thought you hated
these hokey TV specials.
[SAKURA] Uh...
[ELENA] If Sakura
can do it, so can I!
If I budge an inch,
I'll be second place forever!
[ELENA] This is where
the wrestling team,
Berserk, does their training.
Okay, maybe this is scary,
but they'll go easy
on us, I'm sure.
Yeah, right.
Didn't you do your
research on these girls?
According to the info
the agency gave us,
they're serious competitors.
That means none of
that theatrical stuff,
just a heaping helping
of hard knocks.
Some are even ranked
in a world circuit
called 'Shangri-La'.
In other words,
they're hard core.
I'm sure they don't care
if this is a TV show or not.
[SAKURA whimpers]
Now let's go.
[SAKURA] Hm!
[SAKURA] Whoa, this
looks intense already.
[SAKURA] Aaahhh!
Sorry Elena, nice catch.
By the way, why'd you volunteer
for this in the first place?
Oh, uh, mostly 'cause everyone
else was too scared to do it,
and Makoto said wrestling
was really big,
so I figured it would be good
for Sweet Diva's future.
That sounds like
something you'd say.
Even when everyone
else complains,
you always put
Sweet Diva first.
Of course!
Our group is the only place
where I can really be myself!
[ELENA] Heh. That's nice.
All right, check this out.
Fear the might of my
Savage Eagle Pose!
[SAKURA] Stop, we're
gonna get in trouble!
What's wrong?
Can't take the heat?
Are my eagle powers
too real for you?
[KAZAMA] What the
hell are you doing?
[ELENA] Aaahhhhh!
[thud]
[SOUNDMAN 1A]
Hey, isn't that Rio Kazama?
This is a gym, not a damn
daycare, you little turd.
Stop screwing around!
Oh, "little turd" huh?
That's real mature.
[SAKURA] Excuse me.
We're so sorry, we were just
excited to try things out.
[ELENA yells]
[thud]
Is she a wrestler here?
Or just some bitch?
[SAKURA]
For professionals like her,
the ring isn't just a place
to practice-it's their stage.
I'm sure it means
as much to them
as it does to idols like us.
[ASSISTANT DIRECTOR 1A]
Okay, we're going live now.
Please standby.
[CHINATSU] Oh wow,
you're pretty flexible--
that's a nice
start at least!
You think so?
[ELENA] Of course!
If you can dance,
you can do this!
[CAMERAMAN 1A] Wow!
Looking good, Elena!
Are you a secret wrestling fan?
Sweet Diva does this stuff
in practice every day.
We don't use
punching bags,
but idols need strength and
coordination training, too.
[CAMERAMAN 1A] I see.
Looks like pro wrestling's
not so tough after all.
[KAZAMA]
Oh, that's a good one.
A few kicks and
you know it all.
[ELENA] Huh?
I didn't want to just assume
that all idols were bimbos,
but you aren't exactly helping
fight the stereotype here.
Any idiot can hit
a punching bag,
but one good hold
and you'll be crying.
Oh yeah?
Are you picking
a fight with us?
It's pretty sad if
you need to beat up
two total rookies just to
feel good about yourself.
I'm not scared.
I can take as well
as I can dish it out.
Wait a sec.
Let's rock.
[ELENA cries]
[KAZAMA] Crying.
Just like I said.
[ELENA groans]
[KAZAMA]
"Looks like pro wrestling's
not so tough after all!"
[ELENA whimpers]
[ELENA yells]
If it hurts so bad, why don't
you try breaking free?
Piece of cake, right?
[ELENA groans]
Elena, please,
just give up!
"Give up?" No, I'm
through with losing.
I'm here to fight!
Aaahh!
[KAZAMA]
Enough of this crap!
[SAKURA] Elena!
[KAZAMA] She asked for it!
Pro wrestling is for athletes.
You teenyboppers can go home.
Don't play tough.
What I said's true
and you know it.
[MISAKI] Sweet Diva's doing
a pro wrestling tryout?
'Kay, but that's got
nothing to do with me!
You kidding?
Sure course it does!
C'mon Misaki,
I'm a sports journalist
and you're Berserk's
top wrestler!
Put two and two
together here!
[MISAKI sighs]
[MISAKI] Yeah, I'm not that
hot at giving interviews.
These are idols
doing wrestling!
Given your history, nobody would
know better than you what--
Oh, uh, oops.
[MISAKI] I shouldn't
get mad. It's true.
[thud]
What's that?
Well, you've got guts,
for all the good it does you.
Idols are a lot tougher
than you think!
I won't give up 'til
I prove it to you!
Yeah, good luck with all
of that. I'm outta here.
[SAKURA]
Don't run, you coward!
What?
I'm not letting you off
the hook after what you did
to Elena-you get back
here and fight me!
Sakura, but...
Huh. If you're that serious,
then we'll have a real match.
Cabellera contra cabellera.
[gasps]
[SAKURA]
Any time, any place.
In the name of Sweet Diva,
I'm fighting Kazama
from Berserk,
to show her what idols can do!
Well, your choice, your funeral.
[SAKURA] But I wonder what this
"cup o' yellah" thing is about.
In the name of Sweet Diva,
I'm fighting Kazama
from Berserk,
to show her what idols can do!
[MAN 1B gasps]
Hold on! A Cabellera
Contra Cabellera?
Is Sakura serious?
Why in the world
would an idol like her
agree to something like that?
[RECEPTIONIST 1A (F)]
I already told you,
the tickets are sold out.
[CUSTOMER 1A] I drove
all day to get here.
I'm not leaving.
[CUSTOMER 1B] Sweet Diva's
kind of a big deal!
You need a bigger venue!
[CHINATSU] I'm glad you guys
are excited and all
but we aren't selling tickets
here! I'm really sorry!
[KUREA sighs]
[KUREA] So much for
practice today. Jeez.
The idol fans won't be happy
when she gets her
ass handed to her,
but with these kind of
numbers, who really cares?
Wow boss, I think
we're all sold out.
We're setting a new record
for attendance with this one!
[INOBA laughs]
Let's try to keep it up!
[CROWD chatters]
[KAZAMA] Huh.
[SAKURA] I'm ready!
Sorry for making this into
such a big deal, Makoto.
Eh. Ever since you
were a trainee,
you've never given
up on something
once you've committed to it,
so I kind of knew what I
was in for with this one.
I'm so dumb.
I started this mess and
you're cleaning it up.
[SAKURA] It's not
like that at all.
Don't let it bother you.
I'm not just fighting
in your name,
but in the name of idols
everywhere, to defend our honor!
This'll be over in no
time and we can both
put all our energy
into Sweet Diva!
[SAKURA grunts]
[TRAINER 1A (F)] What's wrong?
That all you got?
No, let's do
another round!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)] And
now it's time for the match
you've all been waiting for!
Idols vs wrestlers
in a Cabellera Contra
Cabellera showdown!
Can Sweet Diva's Sakura Hagiwara
show Berserk's Rio Kazama
that she can bust heads as
well as she can bust a move?
[CHAIRMAN] Ready?
[MALE SAKURA FANS]
Super-cute, we love you, Sakura!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
In this corner,
the challenger, Sakura Hagiwara!
[CROWD cheers]
[KAZAMA] Hm.
[SUZUKI]
That chick looks mean!
[TANAKA] You better not
hurt Sakura, you gorilla!
[SAKURA] I know
I'm in over my head,
but being an idol is my pride.
It's my life!
No matter how strong she is,
I can't take this
insult lying down!
I have to show
them I'm serious!
I have to give it
everything I've got!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
There's no telling
how this will end,
but here we go!
[bell dings]
[KAZAMA] Hm?
[SAKURA grunts]
[KANAE] Wow, she really
came out swinging.
It might look bad for
your ladies at Berserk,
but if she wins, it'd make
a hell of a front page story.
You'd better not
get your hopes up.
Give her a beat
down, Sakura!
Yeah! Just do what I would do!
[SAKURA]
I've got this!
What a shame.
Guess you're all talk.
[SAKURA gasps]
I'll show you what a
real kick looks like!
Better brace yourself!
[SAKURA groans]
[KAZAMA] Now let's see,
what shall we do next?
[SAKURA whimpers]
[KAZAMA] Wrestling's not
just about power, you know.
If you don't add some
flair, it's not any fun!
[SAKURA groans]
[SAKURA]
Aaaahhh! Ow!
[AUDIENCE MEMBER 1A]
Come on! Turn it around!
[SAKURA] She's going
to break my hip!
[KAZAMA] Hmph. I like
those screams-keep it up.
Guess idols have
nice voices after all.
[SAKURA] Ahh! It hurts!
[SAKURA yells]
[AUDIENCE MEMBER 1B]
Don't give up, Hagiwara!
It hurts!
[SAKURA cries]
[AUDIENCE MEMBER 1C] Get up!
[KAZAMA] Let's see
how you like this one!
That feel good?
No! That hurts
even worse!
[SAKURA groans]
[SAKURA] I can't breathe.
[thud]
[KAZAMA]
Don't go to sleep yet!
The show's just starting!
[SAKURA groans]
If it hurts so bad, why
don't you tap out already?
[SAKURA whimpers]
[KAZAMA] You know,
I have just the move
for a little tramp like you and
I think the audience will agree!
[SAKURA yells]
[KAZAMA] There you go.
Now show off to all
your little fans.
[CROWD cheers]
No!
Please, stop it!
[gasps]
[KAZAMA FAN 1A] Rio busted out
her famous "Shame Hold!"
Hah! No mercy, same as always!
[KAZAMA FAN 1B]
Thanks, Rio!
Not every day we get
to see a famous idol
with her legs wide open!
[SAKURA] No!
[SAKURA whimpers]
[SAKURA]
They're taking photos!
I don't want to
be seen like this!
Stop!
[SAKURA yells]
Do you finally realize
how weak you are
and how pointless it
is to challenge me?
How 'bout you stop crying
and throw in the towel?
No way!
You'll never make me give up!
I didn't come here to lose!
I see.
Well, you've got conviction,
even if you don't
have any damn sense.
But I have my ways
of making you submit!
[SAKURA groans]
I see-she's putting her
in a sleeper hold.
She's locked in.
It's all over now.
[SAKURA grunts]
[CROWD] Kazama! Kazama!
Kazama! Kazama! Kazama!
[SAKURA]
I don't want to lose!
I don't want to lose.
I don't... want to lose.
No. Don't pass out.
Keep fighting don't--
[bell dings]
[ELENA]
Sakura! Sakura!
[SAKURA]
Huh? Elena?
[ELENA]
C'mon, please! Answer me!
[SAKURA]
Ah! That's right! The match!
[CROWD cheers]
You okay?
[SAKURA]
I lost, didn't I?
I blacked out.
I let everyone down.
[ELENA]
Don't say that.
I thought I could
do it, Elena.
I'm sorry.
[ELENA] Mm-mm.
All right.
Time to hold up your end
of the deal, princess.
What does that mean?
[KAZAMA] I told you.
Cabellera Contra Cabellera.
We might walk out of
this with our lives,
but only one of us
walks out with our hair!
And since you're the loser here,
you know what that means.
[SAKURA gasps]
[ELENA] But am idol's
image is everything!
She's can't chop off her hair
over something stupid like this!
Stupid, is it? [scoffs]
So you idols act tough, but
pussy out in the end, huh?
[SAKURA] I lost fair and square.
I'll keep my word.
[ELENA]
Sakura, no!
I was the one who
challenged you.
Whatever the rules
of the match are,
I have no right to complain.
[ELENA]
Would you stop it?
[KAZAMA]
That's more like it.
Show some backbone.
[ELENA gasps]
Hey look, guys.
[SAKURA cries]
[SAKURA]
I hate this.
Cutting my hair
doesn't even matter.
I'm just so
disappointed in myself.
I couldn't do anything,
and now it's over.
I'm not a wrestler, so I
can't even redeem myself.
I've never felt
like this before.
I want to keep fighting, but...
[KAZAMA] Perfect.
Now beat it.
In the future, just stick
to your tweeny pop crap
and leave the ass-kicking
to us real women, okay?
[NANAMI] Oh my gosh!
[YUHO and AIKA] Sakura!
Don't let this get you down,
it's no big deal!
Just put this whole
stupid thing behind you!
Starting tomorrow,
you'll be our top idol
just like before and none
of this will even matter!
[KAZAMA] Lucky you!
You can't cut it in the ring,
but I'm sure your
brain-dead fans
will welcome you back
without laughing too much.
You and your attention
whore friends can keep
shaking your asses on stage--
at least until you get
too old and they put
all of you out to pasture.
[SAKURA gasps]
[ELENA] Sakura.
[SAKURA] Say what
you want about me.
But I'm not gonna stand for
anyone making fun of Sweet Diva!
Fight me again.
I demand a rematch!
Are you stupid?
I kicked your ass
bad enough already.
I'm not wasting my time
fighting amateurs
'cause of some petty grudge.
[SAKURA] What if I
wasn't an amateur, then?
[KAZAMA] Huh?
I'll go pro if
that's what it takes.
And as a pro wrestler,
I'll challenge you and win!
[GROUP] What?
[KAZAMA] Hmph. Now it's
getting interesting!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)] Whoa!
Didn't see that one coming!
You heard her, folks!
Star idol Sakura Hagiwara
is becoming a pro wrestler!
[KANAE]
Change the whole article!
Here's your headline:
"Sakura Hagiwara's
Big Move to Pro Wrestling!"
That's right!
She lost the battle today,
but in the name of Sweet Diva,
she's going to war against
pro wrestlers everywhere!
[KAZAMA] Hm.
You're kidding.
[KANAE] Hey Chief,
have I got a scoop for you!
The superstar idol,
Sakura Hagiwara
is training to debut
as a pro wrestler!
They're doing some
hard core entrance exam
for her over at Berserk!
Why do I have this
sinking feeling
she's going to
start crying again?
Either way, she's got a
match lined up already!
I don't know if she's
gonna win out there,
but as long as it sells,
I guess it doesn't matter!
So, uh, Sakura,
don't lose too quick.
We want a show.