[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Stand back.
The gong hasn't rung yet.
[SAKURA gasps]
[BLUE PANTHER]
If we've come this far,
there's no need for me
to hide behind this mask.
[SAKURA gasps]
This is wrong.
It can't be!
Elena?!
[CROWD cheers]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Unbelievable!
That's a shocking twist
no one saw coming!
Sharing the ring right
now are two opponents
who used to share the
stage in Sweet Diva!
Sakura Hagiwara
and Elena Miyazawa!
This is insane!
But never mind that,
even more stunning is the
fact that Blue Panther,
the powerhouse that's
been terrorizing Berserk,
is Hagiwara's old friend!
But how? And why?
What she said!
Just what the heck
are you doing here?
Elena?!
I've done all this to get you
to come back to Sweet Diva!
And if I beat you,
you have to retire from
pro wrestling forever!
[SAKURA] Wait.
You're serious, aren't you?
I am, but let's find out
how serious you are.
If you want to
keep on wrestling,
all you have to do is beat me.
And if you do, you're out of
Sweet Diva forever, got it?
[SAKURA] Ah!
[ELENA] Of course,
if you can't beat me,
there's no reason to continue
wrestling, is there?
Let's do this!
[bell dings]
[CROWD cheers]
Elena, no, please wait!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
It's on!
These two used to hit the
top of the charts as singers,
but now they'll hit
each other as wrestlers!
We're about to see how
"un-sweet" these divas can be!
[SAKURA groans]
[MALE FAN 11A]
Put the squeeze on!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Okay, rope break!
[SAKURA yells]
Aaaahhhh!
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA yells]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Miyazawa hits Hagiwara
as hard as she hits
the high notes!
She's made it clear
that her singing voice
isn't the only powerful
thing about her!
[ELENA grunts]
Sakura had challenged
Kazama to a rematch,
and about a week later,
Elena came to me with
a simple request.
She wanted to train at Miyabi.
Elena thought she
was responsible for
Sakura entering the
world of pro wrestling.
As a result, she felt she had to
go through the same experience.
Feel the same pain
as her friend.
[JACKALL] Heh.
[JURI] Elena stayed
true to her word.
Despite her crazy schedule
with her singing career,
she still found time to train.
Each and every day
without fail, in fact.
I was so impressed by her
commitment that I trained her
as I would any other aspiring
wrestler who wanted to go pro.
I mean, it was
the least I could do
for someone with
that kind of spirit.
You know?
[ELENA yells]
[ELENA] Yaah!
[SAKURA groans]
[SUZUKI]
Elena's so strong.
[SAKURA] Wow, she must
have trained really hard.
[ELENA yells]
[SAKURA] Ahh!
[thud]
[SAKURA screams]
[SAKURA] But, why?
[SAKURA yells]
Ow! Not the back!
Aaaahhhhh!
She's in
big trouble!
So what do you think?
Does Sakura stand a chance
against her or what?
I've gotta admit, Sakura
has gotten a lot better.
But after everything her
pop star pal has shown us,
it's not gonna be that easy.
Miss Sakura!
You hang in there!
It hurts so bad!
Ow, ow!
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA] Rope!
That was a close one.
Damn it!
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA yells]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One, two...!
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA]
Aaaaaahhhhh!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara's escape plan
is squashed by the formerly
masked marauder from Miyabi!
It's still anyone's guess as
to why these two are fighting!
Sakura won her rematch
against Rio Kazama,
but despite this,
she announced she was going
to continue to wrestle.
To Elena, this
meant Sweet Diva
would have to go
on without Sakura.
Possibly forever.
She feared that she had
lost her best friend.
That was when Elena knew that
she had to make a decision.
To get Sakura back
to Sweet Diva,
she would have to do it herself.
Elena believed it was her fault
Sakura took up wrestling,
so it was her responsibility
to get her out of it as well.
From that day on, Elena
became the Blue Panther.
She continued training at
Miyabi, but her purpose changed.
It was no longer
to feel the pain
that Sakura was going through.
It was to defeat her, and
force her to rejoin the group.
[SAKURA breathes heavily]
[SAKURA yells]
Aaaahhh!
[JURI] I'll admit her
plan was a bit awkward.
I even had to get personally
involved a few times...
...here and there.
Yes, I think I get it.
That was you dressed
up as Blue Panther,
dismantling Berserk
and challenging Sakura.
And unless I'm mistaken, the
reason you did it was simple.
She reminds you
of someone.
Or to be a bit more accurate,
she reminds you of yourself.
[JURI gasps]
[JACKALL] Juri Sanada
and Misaki Toyoda.
Elena Miyazawa and
Sakura Hagiwara.
Two sides of the same coin,
history repeating itself.
[JACKALL chuckles]
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA] Aaahh!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
The merciless Miyazawa
strikes again!
She isn't cutting
Hagiwara any slack!
[MISAKI] Sakura!
Are you going to keep letting
her smack you around like that?
[SAKURA] Misaki.
She's giving it
all she's got!
So just why the hell
aren't you doing the same?
But she's my friend!
I can't do that!
[MISAKI]
Yes, you can!
Your friend's doing her
best out there for you,
and you're just phoning it in!
Don't get hung up
on the past!
In wrestling you have
to keep moving forward!
[SAKURA gasps]
You wanna be the strongest
in the world, don't you?
Sakura!
Right!
[SAKURA yells]
[ELENA groans]
[SAKURA]
Aaaaaaahhhh!
Uh?
[SAKURA groans]
[SAKURA yells]
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA yells and gasps]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Look at that!
An ankle lock to a
crossed heel hook!
It's not used by Berserk,
so Hagiwara likely isn't trained
to defend against it,
and unfortunately for her,
Elena's technique
is in fine form!
[ELENA grunts]
Ow! Ow, my foot!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara's in a bad place
right now!
[SAKURA yells]
[ELENA grunts]
[ELENA]
How does this feel?
Aaahh! Damn it,
you're breaking my foot!
Aaaaahhh!
[CROWD yells and jeers]
[ELENA grunts]
Please no more!
[SAKURA whimpers]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Okay, rope break!
[MALE FAN 11C]
Keep it goin'!
[SAKURA]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
She's hurt bad.
Crap.
Misaki?
Why you...!
No, not again!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Another takedown from Miyazawa!
She's putting the squeeze
on her former sister in song!
And what a painful
squeeze it is!
[SAKURA screams]
No, I can't!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
You give up, Hagiwara?
[SAKURA] No! No!
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA screams]
Do you give up now, Sakura?
No way!
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA] It hurts!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Hagiwara? Give up?
I don't!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara refuses to surrender!
With her possible retirement
from professional
wrestling at stake,
she's enduring a plethora of
pain to stay in this match!
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA screams]
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Give up?
[SAKURA] No!
[ELENA] No?
[SAKURA screams]
[ELENA] Uh-uh!
I'm gonna end this
here and now, Sakura!
Elena! Aaahh!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Holy headlocks!
Hagiwara is making her
way towards the ropes!
[SAKURA groans]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
But just as she's almost there,
Miyazawa twists her left
knee against the joint!
I can't... take
much more of this!
Come on, you can
do it, Miss Sakura!
Right over here!
A little bit more!
Yeah, that's it!
[SAKURA groans]
Just a little further!
I got it!
Rope break, ref!
Gimme a rope break!
Okay!
[CROWD cheers]
That's a rope break, Miyazawa!
Ease up!
[SAKURA]
Rope! Rope!
[REFEREE 2A (F)] You heard me,
Miyazawa, let her go.
Now!
[ELENA gasps]
[SAKURA whimpers]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
A close escape
by the hurting Hagiwara!
Miss Sakura!
[SAKURA]
Ow! Aaahh!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Miyazawa takes the fight
out of the ring and
straight to Hagiwara!
She's on fire tonight
and isn't showing any
signs of letting up!
[ELENA]
Just give up!
[SAKURA groans]
You jerk!
[KAZAMA]
Are you stupid?
Stay back, Moe!
Elena can be declared the
winner if you interfere
so try to stay cool!
But she's hurt.
[SAKURA groans]
The pain!
Can't take it!
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Ten!
Eleven!
[SAKURA whimpers]
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Twelve!
C'mon, Sakura!
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Thirteen!
[SAKURA] I'm about
to hit my limit.
If she gets me in
another knee bar,
I'm probably down for the count.
[MISAKI] Sakura!
She's gonna try to get you the
moment you step in the ring.
Be careful!
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Sixteen!
Right! Gotcha!
[SAKURA yells]
[SAKURA groans]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
The spider has become the fly!
Miyazawa turned Hagiwara's
own momentum against her
and put her in
another knee bar!
What a stunning display
of skill and finesse!
Ah, dammit!
It's too much!
If you keep it up, you're
gonna twist my leg off!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara's in a vice
that's only getting tighter!
How much more can she take?
Give up yet?
No way!
Oh, yeah?
How about now?
No!
Even with this?
[SAKURA screams]
C'mon, do it, give up!
[ELENA] Sakura, please!
You've got to give up!
If you don't, I have
to keep doing this
and you'll really get hurt!
[SAKURA] I'm never gonna
give up, not now, not ever!
[ELENA gasps]
[SAKURA] Rope!
Referee, rope!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Okay, rope break!
[ELENA breathes heavily]
[MALE FAN 11D] They might
be idols, but those girls
are two of the best pro
wrestlers I've ever seen!
[MALE FAN 11E]
Hey, Elena! You rock!
[MALE FAN 11F] Damn straight!
Now show Sakura who's boss!
[MALE FAN 11G] Elena!
[ELENA grunts]
[ELENA FANS chant]
Elena! Elena!
[MALE FAN 11H] Do it, Sakura!
Kick her butt!
[MALE FAN 11I]
Go Sakura!
[SAKURA FANS chant] Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura! Sakura!
Man, I've never seen
the fans this fired up!
[KANAE chuckles]
Uh oh.
Oh, Elena.
What have you done?
[MISAKI] Juri...
[SAKURA] My leg's not gonna
hold out much longer.
A few more hits like
that and I'm done.
C'mon, shake it off!
Gotta get in there
and give it your all!
[MISAKI] If she gets put
in one more kneebar,
her leg'll fold like
a piece of paper.
Be smart out there.
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara might have the will
to win, but does she
still have the strength?
[ELENA grunts]
Damn it, Sakura, watch out!
No! Please no!
[ELENA yells]
[SAKURA] Now!
[ELENA groans]
[CROWD cheers]
Referee, look,
I've got the pin!
[KAZAMA] Get your head
out of your ass, ref!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One! Two!
[ELENA gasps]
[ELENA] Aaahhh!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Miyazawa escapes
one second away from losing!
If the referee had
gotten in sooner,
Hagiwara would have been
declared the winner!
[MISAKI] Whew, my heart
skipped a beat there.
You almost had her, Sakura.
You can do it again!
[SAKURA yells]
[ELENA screams]
[SAKURA grunts]
[SAKURA] Ow, my knees!
[MISAKI] Come on!
[SAKURA grunts]
[ELENA groans]
No way!
[ELENA yells]
[SAKURA grunts]
[ELENA groans]
Got it!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Okay, rope break!
[SAKURA breathes heavily]
[ELENA groans]
[CROWD] Ooooohh!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
A vengeful Hagiwara's giving
Miyazawa a taste of her own
medicine with a knee bar!
Talk about painful!
Aaaahhh!
You give up yet?
No way!
'Kay! Then what about now?
Aaaaaahhhhh!
Rope!
[ELENA] Sakura.
You're stronger than I thought.
I've only had one
real worry so far.
Her duties to Sweet Diva
have kept her from
focusing on the ring full-time,
and that's left her with little
actual match experience.
And there are things
about wrestling
that can only be taught
in a struggle for victory.
Yes, that's it exactly.
I fear that may be
a weakness for her.
[ELENA groans]
[SAKURA]
Referee, pin!
One! And two!
[SAKURA]
Aaaaaaahhhh!
[ELENA groans]
[SAKURA grunts]
[ELENA yells]
[ELENA whimpers]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One! Two!
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA and ELENA
breathe heavily]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Miyazawa is barely on her feet!
But Hagiwara is looking
pretty pooped, herself.
Wait! I think we know
what that stance means!
[ELENA gasps]
[SAKURA yells]
[CROWD] Ooooohh!
[ELENA groans]
[CROWD cheers]
[KAZAMA] Pin that chump!
[REFEREE 2A (F) and CROWD]
One! Two!
[ELENA grunts]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
After all the damage
Hagiwara's taken to her legs,
her Sakura Special was
lacking some thunder!
[SAKURA yells]
[ELENA] Aaahh!
[ELENA yells]
[SAKURA groans]
[SAKURA gasps]
[ELENA screams]
[SAKURA groans]
[REFEREE 2A (F) and CROWD]
One! Two!
[SAKURA grunts]
[MALE FAN 11K]
That was close!
[ELENA yells]
[SAKURA groans]
Aaaaahh! Aaaaahhh!
[ELENA yells]
[SAKURA groans]
[ELENA groans]
Aahh!
Aaaaahhh!
[ELENA groans]
And right in the face!
C'mon, get her, Sakura!
[SAKURA yells]
[ELENA]
Aaaaahhhh!
[REFEREE 2A (F) and CROWD]
One! Two!
[SAKURA yells]
[ELENA whimpers]
[CROWD cheers]
[REFEREE 2A (F) and CROWD]
One! Two! Thr-!
[ELENA] Aaahh!
Aw, so close!
[SAKURA FANS chant] Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura! Sakura! Sakura!
[SAKURA] All right,
let's finish this!
[ELENA] Heh.
[SAKURA] Eh?
[JURI] Hm.
[ELENA yells]
[MISAKI]
The Juri Crash?
[SAKURA groans]
Aaaaahhh!
No! You've gotta
get out of there!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Miyazawa's back
with a vengeance!
She just performed a Juri Crash
into a Spider Hold,
the same special combo
used by Juri Sanada!
[SAKURA grunts]
I won't quit!
Oh, yeah?
How 'bout now?
[SAKURA groans]
[SAKURA FANS chant]
Sakura! Sakura!
[ELENA FANS chant] Elena!
Elena! Elena! Elena! Elena!
Elena! Elena!
This is getting
hard to watch.
[SAKURA grunts]
[FANS continue chanting]
[ELENA yells]
[SAKURA gasps]
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA whimpers]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Do you give up, Hagiwara?
Aaaahhh!
[SAKURA groans]
Hey, are you okay,
Miss Hagiwara?
Do you want me to
stop the match?
Hagiwara, come on.
You gotta answer me!
[ELENA grunts]
No, Miss Sakura!
Noooooo!
[KANAE] C'mon, Sakura,
you can do it!
You're a real pro wrestler now!
You've gotta get out
of that pin and make
an incredible comeback that'll
drive the audience wild!
I'm rooting for you!
Hey, Chief, you should
cheer her on, too,
while still you have the chance!
She's about to go see the world!
But before that, there's a big
decision she's gotta make,
and it might even be the most
important one of her life!
Sakura, are you gonna
continue wrestling?
Or choose a different path?