[KAZAMA yells]
[KAZAMA] Heh.
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
The threads of fate have drawn
these two together in
a battle for the ages!
Let the gong of
destiny ring high
from heaven to get
this match underway!
[bell dings]
[CROWD cheers]
[KAZAMA]
Aaahh! Eat this!
[KAZAMA] Hm?
Aaahhhh!
[KAZAMA] Huh?
[SAKURA] Aahhhh!
[KAZAMA yells]
[CROWD cheers]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One, two...
[KAZAMA grunts]
[SAKURA] Wait.
Kazama isn't standing up yet?
Well, works for me!
[SAKURA yells]
[KAZAMA] Heh.
[CROWD jeers]
[SAKURA gasps]
Ow!
[KAZAMA] Really giving me
the best you got, huh?
I'll try to return the favor!
[SAKURA groans]
[CROWD yells]
I heard you liked
Boston Crabs,
so I hope this one does
something for you.
Aaahhhh! Aaaahhhh!
[KAZAMA] What's that?
Are those screams
of joy, I hear?
[SAKURA groans]
Ow!
[SAKURA grunts]
[CROWD jeers]
[KAZAMA]
Heh. You can't leave.
The party's just
getting started!
Here we go! Maybe you'll
like this one more!
Now's my chance!
[SAKURA groans]
[KAZAMA grunts]
I'll be damned!
Okay! That's a rope break!
[CROWD yells]
[AUDIENCE GUY 6A]
You'll get her next time, Rio!
[KAZAMA] She really
turned herself around.
If I don't watch it, she's
gonna make a fool out of me.
[SAKURA] I've gotten
a lot stronger,
but her moves hurt
even more now.
And she destroyed
me last time.
Was she going easy on me?
[KAZAMA grunts]
[SAKURA screams]
[KAZAMA]
And one for the road!
[SAKURA yells]
[KAZAMA]
You're gonna love this!
[SAKURA screams]
Aaaahhhh!
I do not love this!
[KAZAMA] She may be
a little tougher,
but one more Boston Crab and
she'll give up like usual!
C'mon idol, let's hear you sing!
A-Aaahhh!
Ow, let me go!
[KAZAMA] You think 9 months
and a string of losses
makes you tough
enough to beat me?
I'll put you in your place,
just like last time!
[SAKURA] Ow!
[KANAE] Damn!
She blocked her path!
Nope!
Nice try, but you won't get
anywhere near that rope!
I'm putting you away!
A-Aaaaaaahhhh!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Do you give up, Hagiwara? No?
[AUDIENCE GUY 6B] Either take
her out or get off, Kazama!
This is boring!
[AUDIENCE GIRL 6A]
Get up, Sakura! You can do it!
[AUDIENCE GUY 6C]
Don't give her an inch, Kazama!
[KAZAMA] You want more?
[AUDIENCE GUY 6D]
Keep the pressure on!
Don't just sit there!
Move, Sakura!
Now, Rio!
Seal the deal!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Hagiwara!
I'm gonna stop the match.
Do you want to give up?
[SAKURA] N-No!
[SAKURA] No!
I'll die before I give up!
You can do it!
Show her what
you're made of!
[SAKURA groans]
What the hell?
This little turd wants a fight!
[SAKURA groans]
Stop acting tough
and give up!
No!
[KAZAMA] You are not
touching that rope!
Aaaaaahhhh! Aaaahhhhh!
Aahh! I can still win!
Stop kidding yourself--
you can't move an inch!
Ow!
[KAZAMA]
What're you gonna do?
Cry me to death?
No way!
I won't give up!
This is not good.
[CROWD cheers]
[SAKURA cries]
[SAKURA] If they've
put their faith in me,
I can't let them down!
If I can't do it for myself,
I have to do it for them!
I have to keep fighting!
[inaudible]
I'm taking you out now!
[SAKURA]
Aaaahhh! Keep fighting!
[KAZAMA grunts]
[CROWD chants] Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura! Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura!
[KAZAMA]
Stop moving!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Still good.
[chanting continues]
Aaahhhhh!
Ref! Rope!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Okay! Rope break!
[KAZAMA grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
[SAKURA breathes heavily]
Not yet.
Ready to play hard ball?
That's fine!
[SAKURA groans]
I'll finish you
with this instead!
[CROWD jeers]
[KANAE]
Another Sleeper Hold!
[MISAKI] That swing is
going to knock her out.
[SAKURA]
What is this move?
I can't breathe!
Too bad I can't
hear you scream,
but it's time to put you to bed!
[SAKURA groans]
[KAZAMA] Sorry, but there's
no coming back from this one!
[SAKURA screams]
[KAZAMA] This is my
rear naked choke!
[SAKURA]
Just keep moving.
If I stop for a
second it's over!
Hey, ref, get over here!
You see?
She's out cold!
Hagiwara?
I'll stop the match!
[KAZAMA chuckles]
Sakura!
Let's go! It's time
to call it, ref!
[KAZAMA chuckles]
[gasps]
Wake up!
[SAKURA] I'm not...
...giving up!
[SAKURA yells]
[KAZAMA] Crap!
She's still not done?
Lose already! You're
being a pain in the ass!
[SAKURA] You think
I'm a pain, huh?
Good! I'll keep it up!
[SAKURA grunts]
[SAKURA] Rope!
Okay! Rope break,
on your feet!
[KAZAMA] Ugh!
She must've trained to
get out of sleepers!
[SAKURA breathes heavily]
[SAKURA]
That was a close one.
The fight ain't
over yet, stupid!
You gonna just stand there?
[KAZAMA yells]
[CROWD] Oooohhh...
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One, two...
[KAZAMA] Just kidding!
I'm not done with you yet!
[SAKURA yells]
Aaahhhh!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One, two...
[SAKURA yells]
[SAKURA] Aaahhh!
[AUDIENCE GUY 6E]
Finish her already!
Okay, I'm sick of you
now, let's end this.
Aaaahhh!
[SAKURA] It's not over.
It's not over!
[KAZAMA] Huh?!
[KAZAMA groans]
[CROWD yells]
[KAZAMA gasps]
Now... it's
payback time!
[SAKURA] Oh, you're
in for it now!
[KAZAMA] Huh?
[SAKURA yells]
How do you like it?!
[KAZAMA yells]
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Kazama?
Give up?
Keep squeezing, baby!
Damn it, get up and move!
[KAZAMA]
Man, screw this crap!
[KAZAMA grunts]
You stay right there!
Aaahhhh! Son of a--
You gonna give up?
[KAZAMA groans]
[KAZAMA] Hell no!
No?!
Then you want some more?
Aaaahhh!
[KAZAMA groans]
Hey ref! See this?
I'm grabbing the rope!
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Okay!
Hagiwara, rope break!
[CROWD cheers]
[SAKURA] How 'bout this one?
Aaahh! Aaaaaahhhh!
[SAKURA grunts]
Hey, Referee, look.
She's out cold!
[KAZAMA grunts]
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Break!
[CROWD cheers]
Finally!
C'mon Sakura, you got this!
[SAKURA] I won't stop
until I win!
[footsteps]
[KAZAMA] Huh?!
[SAKURA] Aaahhhh!
[KAZAMA yells]
One!
Two!
[SUZUKI] I was wrong, Sakura!
I'm sorry I doubted you!
You ready?!
[CROWD cheers]
Make her pay!
[KAZAMA groans]
[SAKURA] Aaahhhh!
[KAZAMA gasps]
One!
[KAZAMA]
What is this crap?
I have four long years'
experience under my belt.
I'm not losing to a rookie!
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Two!
[KAZAMA] You're not
giving up, huh?
[KAZAMA grunts]
Well neither am I,
especially not here!
[SAKURA]
Aahh! Aaaaahhh!
[CROWD yells]
No! How?
There is no damn way...
...I'll ever lose to you.
Got it?
[thud]
[CROWD yells] Whoa!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
A relentless battle and then
a double knock down!
Well, somebody has
to get up, right?
This could decide the winner!
[REFEREE 2A (F)] One!
Two!
[CROWD cheers]
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
[SAKURA]
Elena, Misaki, my friends...
[ELENA]
Sakura! Sakura!
[CROWD cheers]
C'mon already!
Get up!
Don't you want to beat her?
Wow, Elena.
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Seven!
Okay, eight. Nine!
I'm not done here.
Not until I put you away!
You did it!
Well spoken, brat.
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
[AUDIENCE GUY 6F] Hagiwara!
[AUDIENCE GIRL 6B]
Wreck it, Rio!
[AUDIENCE GUY 6G]
I love you, Sakura!
[CROWD cheers]
[KAZAMA] Ah?
[CROWD roars]
Hell yeah!
[YUHO giggles]
Just like old times, huh?
Oh, no way.
Don't know what you're planning
and I don't give a damn.
You are so gonna
eat it, rookie!
[KAZAMA yells]
What the hell?
Here I gooooooo!
[KAZAMA] Aaahhh!
[SAKURA] One more!
[KAZAMA] Aahh!
Is that the...
...Ice Cream Sault!
All right!
[cheers and applause]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara's powerful
two-hit combo nailed
Kazama straight in the jaw!
And speaking of jaws,
mine is gaping wide-I've never
seen anything like that before!
A flying finishing flip!
A Super Sakura Special!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
We may be witnessing the birth
of a new era in
signature strikes!
[SAKURA]
It really worked!
[thudding]
[CHINATSU] Sakura, hurry!
Pin her down!
[REFEREE 2A (F) and CROWD]
One!
Two!
C'mon, Rio!
[REFEREE 2A (F) and CROWD]
And three!
[bell dings]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara has her revenge!
She wins with a pin
after a brutal fight!
The gong is echoing
through the heavens!
This is a victory for the ages!
[CROWD chants] Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura! Sakura...!
I, I really won!
It's over!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
The sixty-sixth match since
her pro debut, a hard-fought,
long-awaited victory!
And judging by the
crowd's response,
one that might have
won her some new fans!
[SAKURA]
I can't believe it!
Everyone is calling my name.
This is pro wrestling.
This is what I've earned with
my blood, sweat, and tears.
This is victory!
I want to win again.
I want to keep fighting.
I want to get
stronger and stronger!
[KUREA] Rio!
Hey! You okay?
Hey, can the
screaming already.
I'm right here, aren't I?
Guess this means
I lost the match, huh?
[KUREA]
You did your best.
Damn lights, they're gonna
make my eyes start watering.
[KAZAMA]
Hey, Hagiwara!
Look, I gotta say,
you're a lot stronger now.
I'll accept my loss today.
And for an idol,
you're pretty damn tough.
But now that you've
beaten me, is that it?
What now?
Back to singing,
like nothing happened?
You went through
all that training
and all that suffering
just for a shot at me?
Is that the kind of
person I lost to?
Over some petty-ass grudge?
Take it easy.
[SAKURA] It was impulsive,
but I did become
a wrestler because Kazama
made fun of Sweet Diva.
So when she says
it's a petty grudge,
that's not far from the truth.
I was so naïve
I thought I could
beat her and be an idol
again in no time.
Obviously, that wasn't the case.
It was a rude awakening.
The world of wrestling was
tougher than I'd ever imagined.
I couldn't accomplish anything.
I was too weak.
I gave up in the ring and I
started to give up on myself.
But it worked
the other way, too.
Once I finally started
getting stronger,
I started getting tougher
on the inside, too,
and I longed for that
feeling more and more.
Now that I've won my battle,
I can put everything
in perspective.
I know who I am now.
Wait, Sakura?
I want to win again!
I want to become
stronger and stronger!
So the truth is...
Pro wrestling has
become very dear to me.
So if I can, I want
to keep fighting!
[ELENA gasps]
[gasps]
[CROWD cheers]
[AUDIENCE GUY 6H]
Damn straight, Hagiwara!
[AUDIENCE GUY 6I]
You're one of us now!
I knew you had it in you!
Oh, Sakura, what
will become of you?
Let us not shed tears,
but be inspired
by the strength of her resolve
and support her ever more,
no matter what path she takes!
This can't be.
[NANAMI] Does that mean she's
quitting the group for good?
That doesn't make sense!
Where's Elena?
I gotta say,
that's good to hear!
You can't just grab a
win and then walk away.
In other words,
I want my revenge.
All right.
Well, it looks like
we're rivals, then!
Thank you, Rio.
[SAKURA] Huh?
[CROWD cheers]
[CROWD chants] Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura! Sakura!
[ELENA sobs]
[KANAE] Why yes, Chief,
I have been drinking!
Why? To celebrate
Sakura's first victory!
Oh, but that's not
even the big news!
You know Jackall Tojo,
the Shangri-la World Champ?
Yeah, well, she's
coming to Japan!
She's sexy, popular
and tough as nails!
Misaki had better watch out,
or she won't stand a
chance in their match.
Did I mention
they have a match?
Whew, I think I need
a cold shower.