[RIVAL WRESTLER GIRL 3A]
Haa!
[SAKURA groans]
Aaaahhh!
Hagiwara, the ropes!
Get to the ropes now!
[SAKURA yells]
Ow!
[SAKURA screams]
I give up!
[scattered applause]
[bell dings]
[CROWD cheers]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)] Sakura
Hagiwara throws in the towel
yet again!
This marks her tenth straight
loss since her debut!
Will this spiral
of defeat ever end?
[SAKURA gasps]
[CHAIRMAN, TANAKA, and SUZUKI]
Super-cute, we love you!
[CHAIRMAN]
Sakura!
What's wrong with you
guys-where's your spirit?
I dunno, it's just...
How long do you think Sakura's
gonna keep up with
this wrestling stuff?
Until she beats
Rio Kazama,
just like she said
after her first match.
Okay sure, but how is
that supposed to happen
when she loses
every single fight?
We're practically
the only fans left now.
Everyone wants her to
go back to Sweet Diva.
That and these matches are
getting pretty hard to watch.
But we have to keep
the hope alive!
[SUZUKI] I hate to say it,
but Sakura's changed.
I'm starting to think
the idol we know and love
might already be gone for good.
No way.
It feels like she gives
up sooner every match.
Obviously, Sakura is cute,
but it was her positive
attitude that made me a fan.
Even if we cheer our
hearts out the whole time,
it feels like a waste.
I mean, with the way she is now,
I doubt she even notices.
[CHAIRMAN] Hey.
[TANAKA] Sorry man,
but I can't take this.
Until things change,
you're on your own.
[CHAIRMAN sighs]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)] In the
blue corner, the hard-luck idol
who's hoping to change her
tune in the ring tonight!
Win or lose,
she's always lovely.
Sakura Hagiwara!
[scattered applause]
We love you!
[SAKURA whimpers]
[thud]
Aaaaahhhh!
It hurts! No!
[SAKURA] When I fought Rio,
I thought things
couldn't get any worse,
but I can't take another
second of this.
I don't want to give up,
but what can I do?
If this is what it
means to be a pro,
I don't know if I can.
[REFEREE 2A (F)] Hagiwara?
I give up.
No more.
[SAKURA gasps]
[BERSERK WRESTLER 2A]
C'mon, c'mon!
[SAKURA whimpers]
I can't take it!
I give up!
[SAKURA yells]
[SAKURA cries]
I give up!
Aaahhh!
[SAKURA cries]
Please stop it!
I give up!
[inaudible]
[CROWD murmurs]
Whenever Misaki is
headlining the event,
there's always a good turnout,
but I'm getting
worried about Sakura.
A 45 fight losing streak would
be devastating for anyone.
[CROWD cheers]
[SAKURA cries and yells]
Ahh!
No, no!
[BERSERK WRESTLER 2E yells]
Aaaaahhhh!
[CROWD groans]
[AUDIENCE GUY 3A]
C'mon. Not this again.
[CROWD yells indistinctly]
[SAKURA yells]
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it! I give up!
[bell dings]
[scattered applause]
[AUDIENCE GUY 3B] No one
wants to see this crap!
If you're not here
to win, just quit!
[CHAIRMAN]
Hey, you shut up!
Sakura's doing her
best out there!
[AUDIENCE GUY 3C] Are you
kidding? She doesn't even care!
[AUDIENCE GUY 3D]
She keeps losing the same way.
It's getting old!
[AUDIENCE GUY 3E]
Stop wasting our time!
[FEMALE FAN 3A]
Don't take it too hard, Sakura!
You can do it!
[SAKURA FANS yell indistinctly]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)] And
Kazama goes for her favorite,
the sleeper hold!
This is gonna be
tough on Suzumoto!
[SAKURA] The only reason I got
into wrestling was to beat Rio.
[AUDIENCE GUY 3E]
Stop wasting our time!
[SAKURA] Even if I'm
standing up for Sweet Diva,
it feels so selfish now.
If I can't even keep
the audience happy,
I have no right to be here.
[BERSERK WRESTLER 2B] Hagiwara!
Misaki's match
is about to start!
Hurry and get to the corner!
Kay! On my way.
[CROWD chatters]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Now, the moment you've all been
waiting for,
tonight's main event!
The BWQ singles title match!
First up, from
the League of Evil,
our challenger, Digger Yamamoto!
[CROWD cheers]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
And next, our reigning champion
from Berserk, the one
and only Misaki Toyoda!
[CROWD cheers]
[FEMALE FAN 3A yells]
[FEMALE FAN 3B]
We love you, Misaki!
[MALE FAN 3A] Marry me!
[FEMALE FANS]
Misaki! Misaki! Misaki!
Wow!
She's so cool!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)] The
League of Evil looks serious!
Will our famous Fighting Artist
from the red corner
defend her crown?
What do you think, guys?
[CROWD cheers]
[bell dings]
[MISAKI grunts]
[thud]
[footsteps]
[MISAKI gasps]
[YAMAMOTO screams]
[YAMAMOTO]
What's wrong, champ?
I didn't know you
were so clumsy!
That's cheating!
I expected her
to play dirty,
but she's trying to shut
Misaki down right off the bat.
[MISAKI groans]
Are you feeling boxed in?
How about a massage?
[MISAKI gasps]
[YAMAMOTO laughs]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Toyoda, give up?
Ugh! No!
[YAMAMOTO] Oh, you want
to play some more?
Get up here, girls!
[MISAKI groans]
[YAMAMOTO] I'm sure you
know our specialty.
The Nightmare Quint Hold!
Aaaaaahhhhh! Aaaahhh!
You're kidding me? Crap!
But that's... not fair!
[SAKURA] There's no way
she can beat five people!
She has to throw in the towel!
[YAMAMOTO]
C'mon, gimme a scream.
[SAKURA]
She's not giving up.
She's thinking of
a way to fight.
[YAMAMOTO chuckles]
[YAMAMOTO] All right!
This is the end!
[MISAKI grunts]
[YAMAMOTO yells]
[LEAGUE OF EVIL 3B]
Oh hell no!
All right, I've
had enough of this.
Hagiwara, back me up, here!
Okay!
[MISAKI] Huh?
Hurry, Miss Toyoda--
now's your chance!
[KANAE] It's over.
Sweet dreams, you troll.
It's the Misaki Special!
One, two, three!
[CROWD cheers and applauds]
[bell dings]
[cheers and applause continue]
[MISAKI laughs]
[SAKURA] Awesome.
Even after all that,
she still won.
[BERSERK WRESTLER 2B]
Of course she did!
Misaki didn't become the champ
by giving up, you know!
You're right.
[MISAKI chuckles]
[SAKURA] This is what it
means to be a pro wrestler!
If I can just be
more like Misaki,
maybe I can turn this around!
[waves crashing]
[pop song plays]
[SAKURA groans]
[bell dings]
Thanks for coming.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks for coming out!
Thanks a lot!
Thank you so much
for supporting us.
[SAKURA yells]
Aaaaahhhh!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
It's the Boston Crab!
Hagiwara's falling into
the same pattern again!
Not good!
[SAKURA groans]
[girls laugh]
[SAKURA yells]
Good night!
Thank you guys, you're the best!
[YUHO]
See you next time, okay?
[cheers and applause]
[SAKURA] I...
I give up.
[bell dings]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)] Sakura
Hagiwara, defeated again!
This marks fifty consecutive
losses since her debut.
These are not the
kinds of records
that Berserk wants
to be setting!
Sakura...
[AUDIENCE GUY 3F]
Just give it up already!
[AUDIENCE GUY 3G]
Nobody likes you!
[AUDIENCE GUY 3H] Go back to you
your old job, you little wimp!
[AUDIENCE GUY 3I]
You suck at everything!
Wow, that's rough.
[SAKURA] First I
let down Sweet Diva,
and now I'm being a
pain to Berserk, too.
I'll go pro if that's
what it takes.
And as a pro wrestler,
I'll challenge you and win!
She insulted idols!
So who better to show
her up than Sweet Diva?
[SAKURA] I quit everything
to be a pro wrestler,
but it's not doing
any good for anyone.
[SAKURA] I can't
do this anymore.
I'm scared of going
back in the ring!
[SAKURA] But if I ran away,
why would they welcome me back?
I did this to myself.
I turned my back on
my friends and my fans
on some selfish whim.
Even if I quit
pro wrestling,
there's nowhere for me
to go back to anymore.
[SAKURA sobs]
[RYO] All right,
give me one more!
[BERSERK WRESTLER 2E]
Yes ma'am!
Hey, Suzumoto, have
you seen Hagiwara?
Huh? That's weird.
No, I haven't seen her today.
Wonder why?
[SAKURA] Even if I
have nowhere to turn.
I can still go back to
being a normal girl, can't I?
They'll forgive me for that.
Right?
[MISAKI] Hagiwara?
Uh--Miss Toyoda...
So, uh, what's going on?
Are you here to train?
Not really, it's more like
prep work for tomorrow's match.
Oh, yeah, hope
everything works out.
I should go.
Hey, can I get a
favor real quick?
[SAKURA] Uh!
[MISAKI] I'd like you to
spar with me a bit tonight.
Huh?
I don't think I'm good enough to
be your partner, Miss Toyoda.
[MISAKI]
Don't be so nervous.
It's not like I'm
challenging you to a match.
No winners, no losers, just two
girls having a nice workout.
I guess.
As long as you don't expect
too much from me, I'll try!
Thanks!
I'm sure you'll do fine!
[MISAKI] Alrighty then,
let's get started.
[SAKURA]
'Kay, here goes nothing!
[MISAKI and SAKURA grunt]
[SAKURA yells]
[SAKURA] She's strong!
She's going to crush me.
I need to try something else!
[SAKURA gasps]
[SAKURA] Turning my own
hold against me, huh?
All right, fine!
[SAKURA] Let's see you
slip out of this one!
Aaahhh!
[SAKURA yells]
[SAKURA] Ah, that hurts!
[SAKURA] She's just doing
the same moves I am,
but she's way stronger!
[SAKURA groans]
Aaaahhhh! Aaahh!
She's too fast.
[SAKURA] My back
can't take this.
[SAKURA groans]
[SAKURA yells]
[SAKURA] I can't move at all!
She's gonna tear me in half!
[SAKURA groans]
Aaahhh!
[SAKURA gasps]
Oh, please no!
[SAKURA screams]
Aaaahhhhhh!
[SAKURA] I think...
I think she almost broke my hip.
[SAKURA screams]
Aaahh! Now what?!
[gasps]
[SAKURA] Anything but this!
[SAKURA groans]
[SAKURA] Every time,
it's the Boston Crab.
Why is she doing this to me?
I can't take this!
Haven't I suffered
enough of these already?
Aaahh!
[SAKURA yells]
[SAKURA groans]
[SAKURA] It's never
hurt this bad before.
I'm going to pass out.
I can't fight back.
I can't even move!
I'm not strong enough!
I'm not good enough!
I'm useless!
[SAKURA whimpers]
[SAKURA] All my friends,
all my fans,
I'm sorry I let you down.
[SAKURA]
I thought I was strong,
but I couldn't keep my promise.
I couldn't accomplish anything.
[SAKURA sobs]
[SAKURA]
Good bye pro wrestling.
Good bye Sweet Diva!
[SAKURA whimpers]
Please stop. I give up!
There's no giving up
in this ring.
[SAKURA gasps]
[MISAKI] The only ones here
right now are you and me,
got it?
There's no crowd,
no referee, and no rules.
If you don't want me
to break your back,
then you stop crying
and do something.
[SAKURA] Oh no.
Aaaahhh!
[KANAE] You heard it here first,
chief, it's all about training!
Well, maybe that's not
exactly breaking news.
I mean, of course
athletes need to train,
but I'm talking about
special training.
Misaki is giving Sakura
a round of it right now,
and I'm expecting big results!
In fact, I have a feeling
we might be seeing
her first win soon!
Forget about Sweet Diva and
give it your all, Sakura!
I'll do some headline
training in the meantime!