[MISAKI]
Hey, you're not done yet.
[SAKURA] Huh?
I want you to
give me ten laps
dashing up and down those
stairs without stopping.
[SAKURA] But...
Can you please let me wait until
I've caught my breath at least?
What, are you insane?
Hell, no!
You're here to learn how
to marshal your strength
and make a comeback even when
it looks like you're beat!
Now go!
Um, yes, ma'am!
Ah!
[SAKURA] Marshal my
strength, and make...
...a comeback!
[STADIUM VOICE 5A]
Are you ready?
[ANNOUNCER 5A (F)] You can feel
the excitement in the air
here at the Japan
Performance Stadium!
With fan favorite
Sakura Hagiwara
trying out pro wrestling,
the position of center stage
vocalist has been vacant.
But that spot will be filled
tonight according to your votes!
[MC (F)] The winner of
the fifth Sweet Diva
Center Vocal Fan Election,
and your new lead singer is...
...Elena Miyazawa!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER 5A (F)]
The fans have spoken!
Elena seizes the group's
coveted center position!
According to votes,
she won by a landslide!
This has been
a long time coming!
Elena's been beaten before
in close call elections
by Sakura Hagiwara,
but now, Elena's finally
come out on top!
This may be
a democracy,
but to Sweet Diva, she's queen!
[ELENA] Wow, lead
vocalist finally.
I almost can't believe it!
But somehow, I still
feel like I haven't won.
Maybe it's because I wasn't
competing against Sakura.
Guess I haven't exactly
beaten her then, have I?
It's not the position
that matters,
it's the accomplishment.
And without my rival here,
what's the point?
[MC (F)]
Congratulations, Elena.
Now that you've
won the election,
is there anything you'd
like to say to the fans?
[CROWD cheers]
[ELENA] Yes.
Thank you.
Thanks so much to each
and every one of you.
Y'know, ever since
the last election...
A lot's happened and there
have been some changes.
Some of you may be happy,
some of you may not.
But let me assure you there's
one thing that won't change.
I promise.
Sweet Diva's commitment to
all its fans won't change!
'Kay?
You're the reason
we do what we do!
I'm gonna make sure the group
keeps giving you our all!
[CROWD cheers]
[MALE FAN 5A] Yeah!
You rock, Elena!
[SATO] We know you will.
We'll follow you forever!
[applause]
[ELENA] Sakura,
hurry back, okay?
[SAKURA screams]
Ow, that hurts!
Well, duh,
of course it hurts!
Tough it out!
Endure and follow
it with a comeback!
Now then, what should
I do to you next?
[CHINATSU groans]
[SAKURA] Aahh!
[CHINATSU] Aahhh!
Now then, what should I...
do to you next?!
[CHINATSU whimpers]
So just endure,
and come back, right?
[CROWD roars]
[SAKURA yells]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara's pinned like an insect
in a kid's bug collection,
and Hornet's about to
put the sting to her!
[HORNET]
Alright, little brat.
Time to feel the sting.
[SAKURA yells]
You're not crawling away!
[FEMALE FAN 5A]
C'mon, Sakura, get up!
[MALE FAN 5B]
Yeah, you can do it!
[MALE FAN 5C]
Stand up, Sakura!
[SAKURA groans]
[HORNET]
Aw, need some help?
Aaaahhh!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
A Camel Clutch using
her bamboo sword!
I've seen some malicious moves
from the League of Evil,
but this takes the cake!
The pop princess
is being decimated
by one of the dirtiest-dealing
divas in the business,
and with an illegal move!
[REFEREE 2A (F)] You have five
seconds to stop, Hornet.
One! Two! Three! Four!
[SAKURA breathes heavily]
[SAKURA yells]
[HORNET] If you thought that
stung, how 'bout this?
[SAKURA groans]
[SAKURA] The pain!
It hurts so bad I want to quit!
But...!
[SAKURA groans]
What?
[SAKURA grunts]
[SAKURA] Endure.
And follow it!
That's one, two,
and three, and four!
[HORNET grunts]
[thud]
[SAKURA] With a comeback!
[SAKURA] Aaahhh!
[HORNET] Aahh!
How 'bout... this?!
[HORNET]
Aaaahhhhh!
[MALE FAN 5D]
Way to go!
[HORNET grunts]
[SAKURA] You're not
crawling away!
[SAKURA yells]
This isn't over!
[HORNET] Aahhh!
She's pinned, ref!
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One! Two!
Oh, no you don't!
[SAKURA yells]
[SAKURA] I can take
things this far.
But I still can't win?
Ah!
[SAKURA screams]
[SAKURA gasps]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One! Two! Three!
[bell dings]
[CROWD cheers]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara loses!
Instead of tearing
Hornet a new one,
she suffered her
sixty-fifth loss!
[SAKURA]
I don't understand it.
I'm so much stronger now.
Thanks to Misaki's training,
I should have been able
to put her away for sure.
[SAKURA] I still
can't win, though.
There's gotta be a reason why.
C'mon, think, what is
it that I'm missing?
[MALE FAN 5E]
Almost there!
[CROWD cheers]
[SAKURA] Uh?
[MALE FAN 5E]
You'll do it next time!
[MALE FAN 5F]
We know you will!
[MALE FAN 5G]
You're fantastic!
[SAKURA] Thank you!
You guys are the best!
[SAKURA] That's right.
I have to do it for the fans!
Excellent fight,
Miss Hagiwara.
Uh! Sorry, I didn't see you.
[INOBA]
And speaking of fights,
I've scheduled your rematch
against Rio Kazama.
[MISAKI sighs]
[punch lands]
[MISAKI] Huh?
Got something
on your mind?
Huh?
Um, no, it's nothing.
[MISAKI] Really?
It's not "I trained so hard
and I'm stronger now,
so why can't I win?"
That sound about right?
Uh!
The whole reason I
became a pro wrestler
was to get a rematch
against Kazama.
Now I've got one.
But I haven't had
a single win yet,
and that makes me wonder if I
even have the right to face her.
Or if it'll be any
different this time.
So in other words,
you're not feeling too confident
about winning, are you?
[SAKURA sighs]
[MISAKI] Look,
there's no such thing
as a sure-fire way
to win, okay?
However, there is a powerful
weapon that might
tip the odds a little bit more
in your favor if you use it.
[SAKURA] Huh?
A special move.
A special move?
[SAKURA]
Oh, wait, I get it,
you mean something like
the Misaki Special?
[MISAKI] Yep.
You don't have a special move,
and that's why you haven't
been able to win yet.
Until you find one,
you'll keep losing.
But my move can't just
be anything, right?
Where do I start?
Like, how do I find it?
[MISAKI] You'll have to
figure that out for yourself.
[SAKURA] Uh!
If you don't figure out your
special move on your own,
then it isn't
really yours, right?
[SAKURA] So I guess
you won't let me use
your Misaki Special, then?
[MISAKI] Uh-uh.
Aw!
[TV VOICE (F)] Special attack!
Earthstar The Rainbow!
A special move.
[CHINATSU] Oh, hey,
good morning, Sakura!
[SAKURA] A special move!
[CHINATSU] Ow! That hurts!
C'mon, cut it out, would ya?
[SAKURA]
A special move...
Holy crap-balls,
what was that about?
It looks like the poor
girl's in a bit of a rut.
Why don't you just give
her a tiny little hint?
Special moves are
the wings that can
lift a wrestler to
victory in the ring.
Those wings have to
be earned, though,
and nobody can put
in the work for her.
[SAKURA] With my size, there's
no way throws will work well
against opponents
larger than me.
And at my weight,
I guess pummels wouldn't
do all that great
against bigger wrestlers,
either, would they?
Gotta find my own special move
outside of the existing ones.
A move that nobody
has ever seen before.
[distant footstep]
[SAKURA] Uh?
[footsteps]
[SAKURA] Elena?
Hi, Sakura.
[SAKURA] Wow, it's been
awhile, hasn't it?
[ELENA] Yeah.
Too long if you ask me.
Sorry to interrupt
your training.
I hope I haven't thrown
you off track or anything.
[SAKURA]
No, it's okay.
Hey, I saw the
last fan election.
That was nice work grabbing
the lead spot this time!
Yeah...
Well, congrats.
I was so happy when they
announced you'd won!
Thanks, Sakura.
But look, the only reason I did
is because you weren't there,
so I don't really feel like
I've won anything at all.
Elena...
Oh, and I was
gonna tell you.
Things have been really
weird without you, Sakura.
For me and everyone
else in the group.
Oh, that reminds me.
My rematch against
Kazama has been set.
[ELENA] What?!
Wow, so it's finally
happening, huh?
[SAKURA] Mm.
[ELENA]
W-Well, that's great!
Once that's done, you're coming
back to Sweet Diva, right?
And you can put this
whole thing behind you.
Yeah, I guess so.
Thank goodness.
To be honest,
I'm pretty nervous.
It's just that I don't know
if I've got what it takes
to win at all, let alone
beat Kazama in a fight.
Sakura.
I know I should be
spending all my time
training right now
instead of worrying.
But no matter how hard I try,
I can't seem to find
whatever it is I need to win.
What should I do?
[ELENA sighs]
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA gasps]
Do what we used to do
whenever we had stage fright!
You remember?
Let's hit it!
Three, two, one, go!
[Pop song plays]
[ELENA laughs]
That's it.
Wow, I didn't realize
how much I needed that!
[ELENA laughs]
[ELENA]
Oh, man, that was fun!
I've really missed singing
and dancing with you!
Are you feeling
any better now?
[SAKURA] Yeah!
Hey, thanks a lot, Elena.
[ELENA]
Don't thank me.
In fact, I should
be apologizing.
[SAKURA] Huh?
[ELENA] I mean,
this mess is all my fault.
[SAKURA] What is?
[ELENA] If it wasn't for what
happened between me and Kazama,
you wouldn't have
left Sweet Diva
and gone into pro wrestling
in the first place.
Elena.
[ELENA] You wouldn't
have gotten hurt.
You wouldn't have
had to go through
all this training, either,
but you did 'cause of me.
No, you've got
it all wrong.
Look, the only person
who's responsible
for my becoming a
wrestler is me, okay?
And if anyone
should be sorry,
it's me for leaving you to carry
Sweet Diva without my help.
Sakura...
What do you know?
I guess you and I've been
thinking the same way.
Elena, would you let everybody
else know I'm gonna do my best
to show Kazama why she
shouldn't mess with pop idols?
[ELENA] Mm. I'll be
there to cheer you on.
[rattling]
[RYO] Are you sure
you want it this high?
Yes! Thank you, Coach!
[KANAE] Some people are
calling this rematch
the "Tussle of the Titans."
What do you think?
Is that apropos?
Wait, "Titans?"
What, are you kidding me?
The only thing titanic about
my opponent are her losses,
and she's about to have
her biggest one yet.
That so?
Well, what do you say about
the rumors that Hagiwara
has stepped up her training
and gotten a lot stronger?
[KAZAMA]
It doesn't matter!
She can keep doing
whatever training she wants
'cause I'm the real pro here.
While that chick
is just a pretender!
[SAKURA grunts]
[KAZAMA yells]
[AIKA]
Night, you guys!
[ELENA]
Yuho! Great job!
You were incredible
out there tonight!
Whoa! I didn't suck?
[both laugh]
Hey, Elena.
[ELENA] Nanami.
You were great, too!
Thanks!
Oh, congrats on getting
it off your chest.
What?
[NANAMI] Whatever's
been bothering you...
[NANAMI giggles]
Nothing gets past you.
I should have known.
So tell me, was it
really that obvious?
[NANAMI]
About as obvious as you
forgetting to wear
makeup tonight.
What?
[NANAMI]
I'm just kidding!
So I hear Sakura's big
rematch is tomorrow night.
[ELENA] Yeah.
And are you gonna go out there
with us and cheer her on?
[ELENA] Huh?
I get it.
You haven't gone to
any of her matches
and that's what's been
bothering you so much
these past few days, hasn't it?
It's just I...
I didn't want to distract
Sakura, that's all.
[NANAMI] But, the
rematch is important.
Yeah, for both of us.
Thanks for being so
understanding, Nanami.
Sakura's not fighting
for herself,
but for the pride of Sweet Diva
and pop idols everywhere.
As our lead vocalist--Mm-mm...
I mean as her friend, I've gotta
be there to cheer her on!
Good to hear!
[Pop song plays]
I just know
Sakura's gonna win!
And once she's done that,
she'll kiss wrestling goodbye
and come back to Sweet Diva!
[YUHO] That's right!
[ELENA gasps]
Huh?
There's no way she'll
lose to that psycho skank!
Yeah, especially if she's
got all of Sweet Diva
there to cheer her on!
Exactly!
And when she's done
with her match,
it'll be a victory celebration
and a welcome back party!
[ELENA laughs]
You know what they say,
all for one!
And one for all,
so let's do it, you guys!
When we come together,
then nothing can stop us!
Let's hear it
for Sweet Diva!
[GROUP] Yeah!
[CROWD murmurs]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
And now for a match
nine months in the making!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)] Sakura
Hagiwara is in the middle
of an unprecedented
losing streak,
but tonight she'll seek revenge
against the master of disaster,
Rio Kazama!
[CROWD cheers]
The air is positively
electric tonight
here inside the Japan
Performance Stadium!
[YUHO]
Geez, you guys.
Our last show here
wasn't this full.
This is insane!
[AIKA] Sakura sure
draws a crowd, huh?
[ELENA] Wow.
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Now coming to the ring
is Sakura Hagiwara!
[intro music plays]
[CROWD cheers]
Yay, Sakura!
Go, Sakura!
[cheers and applause]
[CHAIRMAN] Here we go!
[GROUP]
Super-cute, we love you, Sakura!
Fighting-princess, Sakura!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Now coming to the ring...
...is Rio Kazama!
[intro music plays]
Time to open up
a can of whoop-ass.
[KAZAMA] Heh.
[KAZAMA yells]
[CROWD cheers]
[KAZAMA] Heh.
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Everything in Hagiwara's
wrestling career
has led up to this!
Is she skilled enough
to take on Kazama again?
It's time to find out!
[bell dings]
[KANAE] The big rematch
is finally underway
and Sakura's out for
revenge against Kazama!
It's not going too
well now, though.
I know the odds
are against Sakura
since she's never won, but hey,
stranger things
have happened, right?
So to be safe, keep the front
page open, would ya, Chief?
Wait! What?!
You've got to be kidding!
Sakura, are you sure you're
okay announcing that?
Yikes, the front page
may not have enough room!