[ELENA yells]
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA whimpers]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
Do you give up, Hagiwara?
[ELENA yells]
[SAKURA groans]
Hey, are you okay,
Miss Hagiwara?
Do you want me
to stop the match?
Hagiwara, come on!
You gotta answer me!
No, Miss Sakura!
Nooooo!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara's not moving at all!
Could this be the end?
And the end of her career,
for that matter?
[AUDIENCE GUY 12A] It's not
too late for a comeback!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12B]
Wake up!
[CHAIRMAN] Sakura!
[SAKURA gasps]
Move, Sakura!
Damn it, this match
isn't over yet!
[SAKURA yells]
[CROWD cheers]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
What an escape!
Hagiwara forced herself out
of Miyazawa's Spider Hold
and knocked the wind out
both of them in the process!
[ELENA yells]
[SAKURA screams]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One, two...
[SAKURA grunts]
[ELENA]
Even after all that,
she's still got
some fight in her.
[SAKURA groans]
Aaahh!
[ELENA grunts]
[ELENA gasps]
[CROWD cheers]
Oh wow, that was
one heck of a kick!
Sweet!
Finish her!
[ELENA gasps]
[SAKURA yells]
[ELENA groans]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
The battle rages on!
What an amazing effort
from both wrestlers!
Energy, intensity, and passion
are all on display!
With a beautiful mix of
athleticism and showmanship,
this ring is truly their stage!
[JACKALL] It can be easy to take
these pop idols lightly,
but when they go to battle
with their pride on the line,
it's truly a thing of wonder.
This is more than
just a simple match--
it's real drama and
real excitement!
I daresay it's the finest
form of entertainment
in the entire world.
Juri, if this is part of
some master plan of yours,
you can color me impressed.
Of course not.
They realized their
potential all on their own.
[ELENA gasps]
Aahh!
[SAKURA yells]
[ELENA] You're strong, Sakura.
I know that.
And I know exactly where that
strength comes from, too.
[SAKURA yells]
[ELENA grunts]
[SAKURA groans]
[ELENA yells]
[SAKURA screams]
[ELENA]
You don't want to lose.
I can feel your desire to win
pushing you and pushing you!
Every time you go down,
it gives you the strength
to rise up again!
[SAKURA yells]
[SAKURA screams]
[ELENA] But you
know what, Sakura?
I don't want to lose, either
and whenever you push against me
I'll push back twice as hard!
[ELENA yells]
[SAKURA] Ah!
[ELENA gasps]
Aaaaaahhhhh!
[SAKURA groans]
[CROWD cheers]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara struck back!
That must have done a real
number on her legs,
but it was a sacrifice
she was willing to make
to deflect Miyazawa's
moonsault press!
What determination!
[ELENA yells]
[ELENA groans]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One, two...
[SAKURA] Ahh!
[SAKURA]
Aaaaaahhhh!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Hagiwara pulls off Rio Kazama's
special move, the
Northern Light Bomb!
Not too bad, brat.
[SAKURA grunts]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One, two...
[SAKURA yells]
[chanting] Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura!
[ELENA yells]
[chanting] Elena!
Elena! Elena! Elena!
[KANAE]
Are they crazy?
What, do they think this
is a Sweet Diva Concert?
Please Elena,
please be careful.
[JACKALL chuckles]
Really, Juri.
They know just
what they're doing.
[SAKURA breathes heavily]
[AUDIENCE GUY 12C]
Hagiwara!
[ELENA breathes heavily]
[AUDIENCE GUY 12D] Elena!
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Here it comes!
We all know what
that pose means!
[ELENA gasps]
[SAKURA yells]
[ELENA] Aaahh! Aaaahhh!
[SAKURA screams]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
The Sakura Special!
Her flip was different
this time!
She must've injured
her knee back there!
[ELENA groans]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)] Is she
doing what I think she's doing?
[SAKURA yells]
[SAKURA] Aaahhh!
[ELENA yells]
[gasps]
[REFEREE 2A (F)]
One...
[REFEREE 2A (F) and CROWD]
Two!
Three!
[bell dings]
[CROWD cheers]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
She did it!
Sakura Hagiwara has
done it at last!
A triple spin body press
from her Sakura Special!
After a grueling battle,
her fleet-footed flying
feat has finally
seized the win
from Elena Miyazawa!
[ELENA breathes heavily]
[applauding]
[SAKURA breathes heavily]
[CHAIRMAN, TANAKA, and SUZUKI]
Sakura...
[group laughs]
[MISAKI chuckles]
If that fight went
on any longer,
I'd have had a heart attack.
It's bittersweet.
[INOBA] Huh?
I can't help but wonder if this
was really the best ending.
[INOBA] Hmm...
[SAKURA chuckles]
Sakura...
I guess I lost.
It's all over.
[applause]
She looks upset.
[ELENA sobs]
Elena...
[ELENA] I can't...
I can't take this!
You can call me a coward,
or a sore loser,
or whatever you want,
but I don't want to lose you!
I've suffered enough!
I'm begging you Sakura.
Please! You have to
come back to Sweet Diva!
Elena, I...
I can only be myself
when I'm with you!
Nothing else matters!
Even now!
Even though we were fighting
each other, I really felt alive!
I realized that's my dream!
That if we challenge each other
and challenge ourselves
we can accomplish
something amazing!
As a friend and a rival,
I need you!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12E] We're with
you a hundred percent, Elena!
We wanna see you two
together on stage,
just like before!
[CHAIRMAN]
Whoa, wait, what?
[AUDIENCE GUY 12F] Sakura!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12G]
Come back to Sweet Diva!
[CROWD chants] Sakura! Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura! Sakura! Sakura!
[CROWD] Whhhoooaa!
[CROWD yells]
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
The lead members of Sweet Diva
have all assembled!
This wasn't in
the program, folks,
I'm as surprised as you are!
What am I gonna
do with them?
Look, Elena! You've done
a wonderful job as leader,
but we miss Sakura
just as much as you!
I'm sure all our fans
feel the same way, too!
Even if we can't
fight like you,
we're all here because
we want Sakura back!
You guys.
[YUHO]
Please, Sakura.
You gotta come
back to Sweet Diva!
We're your friends,
aren't we?
Please, let's try
to work it out!
[NANAMI] Mm-hm.
[AUDIENCE GUY 12H]
Yeah! She's right!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12I]
We've been waiting so long
for you to come back!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12J] Can't you
see you belong in Sweet Diva?
I don't--What do I...?
[AUDIENCE GUY 12K]
Don't listen to them, Hagiwara!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12L]
You're finally on a roll!
You can't quit now!
You're awesome!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12M]
Don't leave me!
[MOE]
Miss Sakura!
You won't quit on me, will you?
There's still so much
left for you to see!
Yeah, seriously!
Come on, we gotta do
best two out of three
before you up and quit on us!
[CROWD yells]
Chairman, which side are
we supposed to be on?
Yeah, I'm getting
kinda confused.
Well, whatever she says!
Whatever choice Sakura makes,
we'll support her!
[SAKURA] U-Uh?
[WRESTLING ANNOUNCER (F)]
Whoa, it's Jackall Tojo
and she's got a mic!
The world champion
is making her way
to the center of the arena!
The crowd's gone silent
and all eyes are on her!
Let's see if she has an
answer to this dilemma!
[JACKALL] That was a great match
back there from the both of you-
and it's good to see there's
as much talent and spirit here
as when I got started
in pro wrestling.
So, I've made a decision.
Sakura, your next
stage is the world!
I want you to come to Shangri-La
and truly test yourself!
[SAKURA] Huh?
[AUDIENCE GUY 12N]
Shangri-La?
You think she's world
circuit material?
[AUDIENCE GUY 12P] The champ's
inviting her, isn't she?
If she says so, then
you better believe it!
Besides, you saw her fight!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12Q]
Dude, this is big!
I can't believe
we're here to see this!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12R] You guys
are out of your minds!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12S]
Sakura's gonna tour the world
with Sweet Diva!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12T] Yeah! She's
done enough wrestling already!
That sounds
wonderful, but...
I mean, I'd love to challenge
the world as a pro wrestler.
That's what all of us are
aiming for, I'm sure, but I...
What's the matter?
It's just I don't ever want to
break my ties with Sweet Diva
I love wrestling,
but I can't leave my
friends and fans behind.
You really mean that?
[SAKURA] I'm sorry.
There are just so many
things on my mind.
I don't know what I
want to do anymore.
I think if you step
back and look at things
with a little more confidence,
you'll see that the answer
was obvious from the start.
[SAKURA gasps]
[JACKALL laughs]
[JACKALL] In other words,
just do both of them!
[SAKURA] Huh?
[CROWD murmurs]
Is that even possible?
[JACKALL] You don't
have to decide because
you've got what it takes to
be an idol and a wrestler.
It doesn't matter if you're
on stage or in the ring.
Your energy and your
passion will always
inspire your fans
and make you a star.
Be modest if you like,
but deep down,
you know it's true.
[JACKALL] See?
The answer was right in front
of you this whole time
from the very first day
you stepped in the ring.
[SAKURA] Of course
that would be wonderful,
but I don't know... Do you
really think I can do it?
[JACKALL] It's not a matter
of "can" or "can't."
Stop worrying and just do it!
If they're both
so important to you
that you can't let either go,
you have to find the
strength to do both
If it really means so much,
you'll find a way!
But you can't question if
you can pull it off or not
you just have to let
loose and give it a shot!
It's time for you
to decide, Sakura.
Do you wanna be the best
in the world, or not?
[CHAIRMAN]
You can do it!
You can't give up now, Sakura!
You'll be the best idol
and the best wrestler!
We'll all be cheering
for you the whole way!
Sakura! Sakura!
[CROWD chants] Sakura! Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura! Sakura! Sakura!
Wow.
[group chuckles]
Do you really think...?
[ELENA] Sakura.
I'm here for you, partner.
If anyone can pull
this off, it's you.
[SAKURA] Elena.
[JURI] Don't sell
yourself short.
[ELENA and SAKURA gasps]
Look, I want you
in on this too, Elena.
I know you have
the potential.
Besides, the two of you
are rivals, aren't you?
Well yeah, but--
[JACKALL] I think we have room
in Shangri-La for one more.
You're already taking on
the world with Sweet Diva,
so why not?
You may be a little rough
around the edges now,
but once we pound
you into shape,
you'll be shining like
a diamond in no time.
[ELENA] B-But I...
I didn't ask for this.
The only reason I
entered the ring at all
was because I
wanted Sakura back.
Besides, if I expected Sakura
to retire after losing,
then so should I.
[JURI] That's ridiculous.
There's no reason for
you to lie to yourself.
[ELENA]
Wh-What do you mean?
This match was about more than
just getting your friend back.
I saw the way you
were fighting just now.
You didn't push yourself
to win a silly wager
you did it because you have
the spirit of a true wrestler.
[ELENA gasps]
[JURI] In other words,
you're already one of us.
[CROWD cheers]
[AUDIENCE GUY 12O]
Listen to her, Miyazawa!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12D]
I wanna see you fight again!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12E]
You can be an idol too,
but don't quit wrestling!
[CROWD chants] Elena!
Elena! Elena! Elena!
Well ladies,
I think it's official.
The audience has spoken.
Now it's time to be honest with
them and honest with yourself.
[chanting continues]
[JACKALL]
Chop, chop!
Don't keep the crowd waiting!
It sounds like they're
ready for your answer.
Isn't that right, you guys?
[CROWD cheers]
[AUDIENCE GUY 12G] Yeah!
Let's hear it!
Come on, everybody!
[AUDIENCE GUY 12I]
Don't leave me hanging!
[SAKURA and ELENA chuckle]
[SAKURA] Whether it's
singing or wrestling,
we feel just as
strongly as all of you.
Choosing one is impossible.
And after all the two
of us have been through,
how could we ever
give up either of them?
[SAKURA] So even if it's
hard we'll keep fighting.
And we'll try our best
not to let down any fans!
I promise you, this is
only the beginning!
As idols and wrestlers,
we'll never stop improving.
[SAKURA and ELENA chuckle]
And that's because...
...we're gonna be the
strongest in the world!
[cheers and applause]
[JURI]
Misaki? Kanae?
[SAKURA and ELENA giggle]
Those two might just
steal your throne.
Don't try to make me
feel like an old lady.
We're just getting started!
We've seen them fight,
now let's give them
a chance to sing!
Wait, what?
You mean now?
[SAKURA and ELENA gasp]
[SAKURA] Guys!
If you want to try both,
now's a good time to start!
Then let's do it!
[CROWD cheers]
[girls laugh]
Miss Sakura even makes
idols look awesome!
I wonder if I could do that?
[AIKA and YUHO] Yay!
How long do you think it'll
take to get to the arena?
Ten minutes jogging, five
minutes going full throttle!
[SAKURA] Bet I can
make it in four!
I'll race you!
Okay, you're on,
but don't blame me
if you're all out of breath
for the big match!
What do you take me for,
some kind of wimp?
I guess we'll find out,
won't we?
No bruises where the
audience can see, okay?
You still have a concert
after the match!
[SAKURA and ELENA]
Yes ma'am!
[ELENA laughs]
[SAKURA and ELENA]
Let's get this show on the road!
[bell dings]
[SAKURA] Thanks for cheering
me on until the end, you guys!
As you may have heard,
Sweet Diva is
launching a world tour
and I'm returning to sing
and dance along with them!
We might even come
to your country next!
Also, there's an invitation
only event coming up!
We'll show a secret code
and phone number to call
during my next wrestling match,
so be ready if you want a
chance to win free tickets!
As always, if you don't get
Berserk Wrestling in your area,
contact your cable provider!