[ROSETTE] Jeepers,
why aren't we there yet?
Just how much longer
is this gonna take?
I'm pretty sure that we're
heading in the right direction.
Chrono, you're holding
that upside down.
Hey, what's eating you, anyway?
Pull yourself together.
[CHRONO] Right.
If we could just hitch
a ride from someone,
we'd make it to San Francisco
in no time flat.
But there isn't
anyone else around.
[CHRONO] It looks like there's
a service station up ahead,
so why don't we
just stick with it.
All right!
[AZMARIA] Oh.
[AZMARIA] Huh?
Is that a...?
It couldn't be.
Lucky us!
Hey! Over here!
Hey, stop for us!
Hey!
They didn't even slow down!
Chrono, this is all your fault!
If you had been holding
the map right-side up...
[CHRONO] Hey, don't
take it all out on me!
Rosette,
look behind you.
Eh? Ahh!
Ahhh!
[coughing]
Huh?
Ahh! Satella!
What are you doing way out here
in the middle of nowhere?
What I do and where I do it
is no concern of yours.
It's quite astounding,
but you three are even
dirtier than usual.
[ROSETTE grunts angrily]
[AZMARIA] Oh, Miss Satella,
you're always so beautiful.
Ah, your honesty
is refreshing.
Perhaps I should reward you
with an invitation to my villa.
Azmaria is incredible,
already cozying up to the
rich folk, for crying out loud.
Miss Satella,
you're a life saver.
Really, thanks.
It's amazing,
you were actually
planning to walk all
the way to San Francisco?
It's not like
we had a choice.
We lost everything
when our luggage got
carried off on that train.
[SATELLA] Hmm. Could it be
that you're all penniless?
Well excuse us, Princess,
but unlike you,
we're all a little strapped
for time and money!
Well, I don't really have
any time to spare either,
but I do have more than
enough money to burn.
[ROSETTE grunts angrily]
[CHRONO] Cut it out, Rosette!
We might get the bum's rush!
[SATELLA] Why don't
you just sit quietly?
[AZMARIA]
Oh! It's San Francisco!
Please wake up, Rosette!
Rosette! Wake up!
Huh?
Huh? We're there?
[AZMARIA] Come on, Chrono!
Come and see!
Sorry, you go on.
I'll be there in a second.
Oh, I see.
Okay, we'll be waiting.
Wow!
[STEINER]
Yes, this is the best point
from which to view
San Francisco.
[ROSETTE] We made it.
Joshua is somewhere
in this town.
Right! Let's do it!
Chrono! Jeepers creepers,
how long does it
take you to wake up?!
We're finally here,
but we can't do anything
until you snap out of it!
Ahhh!
Chrono! What are you doing?!
[SATELLA] Kommen sie!
Rip him to shreds!
Mutigster!
Erlöschen!
Whoa. That hurt.
Chrono sure is a lot bolder
than he looks, isn't he?
Heh heh. Just what was
he thinking, anyway?
Exactly what kind of training
are you giving him?!
Now, now, I'll be sure
to firmly scold him.
But he's a devil!
[AZMARIA] Rosette!
It's horrible!
He's passed out.
[ROSETTE] What?
And he has a
horribly high fever.
Huh?
A fever?
Well slap on a bandage,
and I'm sure he'll be jake.
Miss Satella,
could you please
take us to the
Magdalene branch office?
Uh. Of course, but I...
If I may, might I suggest
that we take him to Miss
Satella's villa instead?
I believe that it
would be much closer.
[AZMARIA] Oh yes, please, sir!
I'm sorry, Rosette.
We're so close to
finding Joshua, but I...
What are you talking about?
When you're sick you don't have
to worry about things like that.
Right now, the most important
thing is for you to get better.
[SATELLA] So, how is he?
[ROSETTE] He's asleep.
Azmaria and Steiner
are with him right now.
[SATELLA] Ah.
[ROSETTE sighs]
I don't think Chrono's
ever had a fever before.
I suspect that his
legion sense is activating.
[ROSETTE] Legion?
His body's constructed
like other devils, right?
[SATELLA] When they take damage,
a devil's legion power works to
restore their health rapidly.
[ROSETTE] Wah!
[SATELLA] Are you listening
to what I'm saying?!
[ROSETTE]
Listening...
Oh yeah, right.
We just need to bring
down his fever, right?
Okay, now we're
on the trolley!
Ha, ha, ha!
I'm gonna buy a fever reducer!
God, what a simple girl.
Miss Satella, did I just hear
Rosette go out the front door?
Well, yes.
You mean you let her
go all by herself?
Yeah, why not?
Uh? Ahh!
[SATELLA] Seriously, you don't
even know where the pharmacy is,
so why did you
run off like that?
I couldn't help myself.
I'm just impulsive.
Haven't you ever considered the
idea of thinking before you act?
And exactly how long
are you planning
to wear those filthy rags?
[ROSETTE] Ugh.
You're going to rot if
you don't change soon.
I don't need advice from you!
Ah! Sit down,
you're too close!
Heh. But you know, you're
a lot nicer than I thought.
I wouldn't have expected
you to help me like this.
What are you talking about?
I only came with you to make
sure it gets done quickly!
All I want is for Chrono to
get well as soon as possible,
so you can all hurry up
and get out of my house!
[ROSETTE] Hah! You won't
have to say anything.
We'll be happy to leave.
[SATELLA] Well, here we are.
In here?
Yeah. They usually have
most medicines in stock.
[SHOPKEEPER] Take care!
[SHOPKEEPER] Are you looking
for something, miss?
Ah! Well, yes sir.
[SHOPKEEPER] And what
is it you're looking for?
Well, um...
[SHOPKEEPER] Please, tell me.
[ROSETTE laughs]
[SHOPKEEPER laughs]
Ahh!
Hurry up and tell
him what you want!
Okay already.
Do you have a fever
reducer that would work...
...even on a devil?
I'm sorry, w-what
did you just say?
[SATELLA] Sorry to
have bothered you!
[SHOPKEEPER sighs]
[ROSETTE] O-Ow!
Let me go, you pill!
What kind of idiot would
say something like that?
What was I supposed to say?
There are lots of
other ways to say it.
By the way, this is
medicine for Chrono.
A normal store won't have it!
[SATELLA] Yeah, I've heard this
shop has a good reputation.
[ROSETTE] Hmm...
Hey, doesn't this store
look closed? It's dark.
Well, it's not
supposed to be.
It's open.
[SATELLA gasps]
[ROSETTE] Ah!
What's with this place?
[door creaks]
[gasps]
It won't open! It's locked!
Ah! Wait a second, why?
[ROSETTE and SATELLA scream]
[SHOPKEEPER B]
I'm sorry, ladies.
I certainly didn't
mean to scare you.
That would
scare anyone!
[SHOPKEEPER B]
Now, now, let's see,
a powerful fever reducer that
would work, even on a devil.
Was that right?
Choose whichever ones you like.
Uhh...
Do you have something that might
be a little easier to take?
[SHOPKEEPER B] Hm?
Easier to take, huh?
Then this would be
my recommendation.
Ahhh!
[ROSETTE] What was that?
There's absolutely no
way I'd give Chrono that.
Well that was
a waste of time.
Let's go home now.
Huh? Wait
just a second.
We haven't tried all of
the pharmacies yet, have we?
It makes no difference,
they're all the same.
[ROSETTE] Wait!
What are you doing?
They're not all the same!
Ach, I guess I understand.
Please, isn't there
something you can do?
[SHOPKEEPER laughs]
[ROSETTE sighs]
[SHOPKEEPER C] Beat it, kid!
[SATELLA] Just give up.
No matter where we go, no one
is going to take you seriously.
Besides, I don't think there
are any medicines for devils.
Now magic maybe...
Magic?
[SATELLA] Wait a second,
what exactly are we doing
in a place like this?
[ROSETTE] I have an idea.
[SATELLA] Huh? Hey wait!
What are you doing
stopping all of a sudden?
[ROSETTE] Ha, ha!
Satella, I'm going
in here, okay?
Fortunes told?
[OLD WOMAN]
The reflection of your destiny
will be revealed to me,
and then I shall give you
the guidance that you desire.
So, shall I look?
You betcha!
And fast.
Ohh! Ohh!
[ROSETTE]
Granny? Um... Granny?
What are you seeing?
Oh, well the future is tricky
and sometimes it can
be difficult to see.
And by the way,
according to reflection,
there is an important ally
or close friend who is ill.
Is this so?
Yes.
His fever is causing
horrible nightmares.
Let me tell you a charm to
reduce his fever... no charge.
[ROSETTE] Huh?
[OLD WOMAN whispers]
Huh?!
Wait a second! Wait for me!
Ah, oh what an
unfortunate destiny.
[ROSETTE] We're here!
[AZMARIA gasps]
Welcome back!
So, has Chrono
gotten any better?
No, he's still asleep.
I see.
So um, did they
have any medicine?
Truly, it was
sheer madness.
She mercilessly dragged
me all over the place,
and she even made me go
with her to a fortune teller.
Now I'm exhausted,
and all we bought was
this normal cold medicine.
Oh, I see.
What did the fortune teller
say was in your future, Rosette?
[ROSETTE] Ack.
[SATELLA] A charm
for reducing fevers.
A charm?
Uh, I almost forgot, I have
to get our dinner ready!
[ROSETTE laughs]
[SATELLA] Hm?
My God, what is it
with you three, anyway?!
[SATELLA yells in German]
You're not going to
tell me that you have
a fever now, too, are you?
She feels hot!
Huh?
[SATELLA] Seriously...
It's unbelievable, what are
we going to do with you?
Wait on me hand and foot?
[ROSETTE sobs]
This isn't funny.
You're a meanie.
[SATELLA]
Hurry up and go to sleep.
[AZMARIA]
Rosette, are you all right?
[ROSETTE snores]
Huh? You're going to make it?
[AZMARIA] Yes, ma'am.
It's important for
me to do my part
to help Rosette and Chrono, too.
Oh Steiner?
[STEINER] Yes milady?
[AZMARIA] It's all right.
Please let me do it by myself.
[AZMARIA] All right.
This is my big chance!
[shattering sound]
Huh?
Are you all right, miss?
Ahh!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Don't worry, at least
you weren't hurt.
[AZMARIA] Yes, ma'am.
[crashing sound]
[AZMARIA] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry...
[SATELLA] Are you sure
you're going to be all right?
[ROSETTE snores]
[AZMARIA] It's ready!
It's incredible, Azmaria!
I really hope
they like it!
Don't you worry! I'm sure
they will be delighted.
Let's take it to them,
before it gets cold!
Okay.
[knocking]
[AZMARIA] Chrono?
[CHRONO] Huh?
So, are you feeling better?
[CHRONO] Azmaria?
Your fever hasn't
gone down yet.
It's important for you
to eat something,
so you can feel better.
Oh wow, did you make
all this yourself, Azmaria?
I'm not sure if
you'll like it.
It's delicious.
Ah! Thank goodness!
Well, then please,
take your time eating it,
and I'll come back for
the dishes later, okay.
Thanks a lot, Azmaria.
Ah! Azmaria...
Uh-huh?
Where's Rosette?
Uh, well I... uh...
Huh?
[eats noisily]
Ha, ha, ha.
Slow down, you
mustn't eat so fast!
[CHRONO] What? A fever?!
But her appetite's
as healthy as ever.
That is our Rosette.
Yeah.
[ROSETTE] Ah!
Mm. That was delicious!
Are you sure
that you are sick?
Oh Satella,
how's Chrono doing?
I don't think his
fever is coming down.
Regular medicine doesn't
seem strong enough.
What's wrong?
[ROSETTE]
I'm just not myself.
[SATELLA] Hm?
I need him to
get better soon.
Could it be... you two...
It's just that it's
so hard to carry bags.
Huh?
[ROSETTE yawns]
I get so tired. This town
is straight up and down.
What is Chrono, your servant?
It's just that we can't
go looking for Joshua
until Chrono gets better,
what a bother.
[snoring]
[SATELLA sighs]
[SATELLA] Honestly,
she is such an appalling girl.
I'm sure she's
only acting that way
because she's
worried about Chrono.
[SATELLA] What?
I know you can't tell
by the way she acts,
and she'll never say it...
But it's true.
And of course Chrono's
always worrying about Rosette.
Even when they're apart,
they never stop
thinking about each other,
and that's wonderful.
Maybe that's the answer.
I believe the best
medicine for Chrono
would be if he had Rosette
sitting there with him,
right by his side.
[SATELLA] Wait! Azmaria!
Oh no, not you too!
She is resting
now, milady.
So, then she was
just very tired.
Mhmm.
Thank goodness,
I was worried that she'd
come down with a fever, too.
Yes, I was quite worried
about her as well.
[STEINER] Milady.
[SATELLA] Mhmm.
They are excellent
friends, are they not?
Well, they're not
exactly my friends.
It's turned out to be
a good day, hasn't it?
[STEINER] All that remains
now is for Mr. Chrono
to recover from his illness.
[door opens]
[STEINER] Hmm?
[door closes]
Oh, Rosette. I hope that
at least you're feeling better.
You should be thinking about
your own health, Chrono.
I'll be all right if I...
can just get... some rest.
I'm sorry, Rosette.
A charm to
reduce his fever.
[whispering]
Hey, Chrono.
[wind blows]
[CHRONO] Rosette.
Sorry I caused
so much trouble.
Chrono, why you!
[CHRONO] Ah!
How dare you make me
worry like that...
[AZMARIA] Well, it looks
like they feel better.
[ROSETTE] I didn't have any
idea what I was going to do.
Thank goodness!
[CHRONO yells]
[bell rings]
Who may I say is calling?
[DUFFAU] I seek the
one known as Chrono.
[SATELLA] I'm an art dealer,
so I encounter a
variety of customers.
However, I absolutely
refuse to serve a devil!
[ROSETTE] But he seems
harmless enough.
Let's at least hear
what he has to say.
[SATELLA]
Then do it elsewhere!
Remember, he's a devil,
not a person.
[STEINER] Milady, would
Darjeeling be an acceptable
choice for the tea?
[SATELLA] Water should
be quite adequate.
And keep him out of
the drawing room!
[ROSETTE]
Next episode, "Pursuer."
[SATELLA] Chrono, stop!
That's my prized Wedgwood china!