[thunder]
[bell rings]
I understand that the one
known as Chrono is here.
My apologies, but who
might I say is asking?
[STEINER] Hmm.
[DUFFAU] Just tell him,
"The Duke is here."
[CHRONO] Duffau!
Chrono?
[gasps]
[ROSETTE] A devil.
[lightning]
That's right, and this
one's a pursuer.
Steiner, back
away from him.
Such a rash child!
I am not here to fight.
Not with you.
[CHRONO] What?
[DUFFAU] We are all incomplete
creations, Sinner Chrono.
And you humans as well...
all cursed by
the number six.
Hence, we have
a common foe.
A common foe?
Let us join together to
defeat the Sinner Aion!
And for the sake of
retrieving the lost darkness.
Place the head of Pandemonium
back beneath the earth.
Therefore, I extend the olive
branch and ask for your help.
[CHAIRMAN] No, we cannot
approve of this.
For we who serve the Lord,
to work together with
these creatures is absolutely
out of the question.
But sir, in this case,
isn't it possible
that they have no choice
except to seek our aid?
Even so, it is in their
nature to use this
to further their own agendas.
They are what they are.
It is my understanding
that the one called Duffau
holds the status of a duke
and wields great influence
in the realm of Pandemonium.
I believe we should listen quite
carefully to what he has to say.
[CHAIRMAN sighs]
[CHAIRMAN] It was the New York
branch's acceptance
of a non-human that caused
this to come to pass.
[KATE] We are well
aware of that, sir.
However, there are other things
we would have you bear in mind.
[CHAIRMAN] Then enlighten us,
Sister Kate.
Chrono's contributions
to the Order of Magdalene
have not been small.
It's thanks to his efforts that
so many cases have been closed.
And actually this
could prove to be
an excellent opportunity
for us as well.
[CHAIRMAN] Hmm?
[REMINGTON] Until now,
our ability to obtain
information concerning
Aion and his plans
has been limited to scraps of
intelligence and pure deduction.
But no longer.
This alliance
could prove to be
an invaluable font
of information!
And I say we
should accept!
[COUNCILMEN murmur]
[KATE] For us to simply say that
his kind betrayed our Lord
and judge on
that basis alone,
would be bias of
the worst order.
It was Chrono and
our Sister Rosette
who taught us the
truth of that lesson.
And in this judgment,
I shall trust them completely.
This could be the worst judgment
since the fruit of knowledge.
We must have the courage
to take this step forward.
[CHAIRMAN chuckles]
Do you know...
...how much like
Rosette you've become?
[KATE] Hmm?
[REMINGTON chuckles]
You never learn anything
if you never try anything.
I think that's what she'd
say if she were in my shoes.
[GURIO] Great Lord Duffau.
How fares Pandemonium?
[CARV] I couldn't keep my
eyes open. Too much light.
I see.
[GURIO] And what
of Chrono, Lord?
[DUFFAU] We shall
wait until dusk.
He'll come with
their answer then.
Those clothes look
quite nice on you.
Oh, these things?
I borrowed them from
Satella's closet.
The council finally
contacted us, you know?
Then did Sister Kate
say what we...
She said that she's
leaving it up to us.
The council's
not on board yet,
but she said she'll
handle it somehow.
It's so strange.
Even this far away,
I'm still causing problems
for poor Sister Kate.
Oh, but that's not
true at all, Rosette!
You know, I don't
even know why.
[AZMARIA] Huh?
When I heard those other demons
calling Chrono a Sinner,
I never asked him why.
[clock ticks]
[SATELLA] The head of
Pandemonium he said.
[CHRONO] Huh?
So explain please.
Your bearded friend
was quite discrete,
but I want to know what
it was you Sinners did.
[CHRONO sighs]
[AION] Let us go!
The free world awaits!
[CHRONO] Aion, that's...
[AION] Yes. Pandemonium's head.
This is a revolution, after all.
The era of the old guard
shall end today!
We're going to destroy eternity!
Aion, how...
[SHADER] Uh-uh you're late!
Just what have you
been up to, Chrono?
Sh-Sh-Shader...
[AION] So, you came.
[SHADER] Bah!
We can't be doing this...
It's time to take
the plunge at last!
[CHRONO] Our dream...
[AION] That's right.
And you'll do anything as long
as it's for our dream.
But is this cause true?
[VIEDE] Hey! Aion!
Let's do this already!
Time to kill.
No more killing time.
[laughs]
Chrono, I'll ask once more.
Are you prepared
to take the plunge?
[CHRONO exhales]
Music to my ears...
[CHRONO] The one that
fell from Heaven...
...became Pandemonium.
[SATELLA gasps]
An angel? You don't mean...
Pandemonium hated God
with all its being
and granted knowledge
to man, made in His image.
Heaven, Earth, and man formed
a never-ending cycle
of faith and hatred,
and changed into the
order we call this world.
[SATELLA] What? That...
[CHRONO] Aion said that he
wanted to change this order...
...to create a world where
desire is not a sin.
When desire is born,
then and only then,
will hope shine.
In the same way,
devils must exist,
so we can see the holiness
and authority of God.
That's why Aion said he wanted
to be free of Heaven's yoke.
[AION] Let us go!
The free world awaits.
But in truth, the price
of freedom was...
Looking back, I can see
that's what Aion wanted.
[ROSETTE] Huh?
[AION laughs]
Aion, what have you done?!
Ahh, why such a
long face, Chrono?
Can't you see this leaves
no one to challenge us?
[AION] Look at her...
Pandemonium can't say
anything... not anymore.
We are free!
You're going to
destroy the darkness!
[RIZEL] Why are you
getting so mad, Chrono?
Burn it. It's going to burn...
This is great!
I'm so excited!
This is all going to
be such fun, oh yes!
[CHRONO] Duffau...
You bastards! Don't you
realize the consequences
of what you've done?
You're a bit too late, Duffau.
So, Aion, it was you.
[AION laughs]
I was wondering when those
old bats would show up.
Old bats? Ha! They look
like sitting ducks to me.
And I say they can drop dead!
[roaring]
[AION] It's time, Chrono.
You're an accomplice now.
It's with us or against us.
[SHADER] That smarts!
[DUFFAU] You're mine!
[CHRONO] Aion!
[DUFFAU] Chrono, put the head
back while there's still time!
This is a revolution,
you old fool!
[DUFFAU] Can't you fools
see what you've done?
Attack and slay them all!
Don't leave a single one alive!
Ahhhh!
Ah! Woolen bloomers!
Heading to Frisco, are you?
Uh-huh! Sister Kate's
sending us.
She told us we're supposed to
support Rosette any way we can.
[ELDER] Ah, yes.
And speaking of Rosette,
I've brought some good
luck charms for her.
I fear that the
fight will probably
only get fiercer from here,
so with that in mind,
I've whipped up
some new Gospel-specific
automatic clips for her.
And of course,
I've put together
a supply for you three
lovelies as well.
Thank you so
very much, sir.
Rosette will be
as happy as we are.
You girls stay firm
out there, all right?
Right!
We were hand-picked
by Father Remington
specifically for this mission.
So we understand
exactly what it is
we're getting into,
Elder, sir.
And we're gonna
go give 'em Hell!
Ooohhh! I'm so proud.
But things are going to get
awfully lonely around here.
Oh Elder...
[girls yell]
Oh, you've all grown up
so magnificently.
I want you to
keep me abreast...
For Heaven's sake, sir!
The Virgin's watching,
you pervert!
[thonk]
[ELDER] Lord, please
forgive these girls
who would strike
a helpless old man!
[CLAIRE] The Lord works
in mysterious ways!
[thonk]
[car approaches]
[GILLIAM] My name is Gilliam,
from the Order of Magdalene's
west coast branch.
Sister Kate asked me to come,
to serve as a witness,
and to help you
in any way I can.
I've also brought a complete
set of militia equipment
to replace yours.
They, and I, am
at your service.
Thank you for the offer, sir.
I'm Sister Rosette.
And you would be
Chrono, correct?
I've repaired your equipment
kit and brought that as well.
[DUFFAU] So, have you
come to a conclusion?
Yes, the Order of Magdalene
will abide by Rosette
and Chrono's decision.
[AION] Ah. Can you hear it?
It's the call of desire.
Such a lovely era...
Lady Shader
has sent word.
The preparations
are complete, sir.
[SHADER] Hmm?
Oh, good morning!
Darling, sweet Fi my dear.
Ah!
Thank you... Sister.
My, oh my.
You are close.
[AION] Enough. Show me.
Yes, sir!
[SHADER] As you can see,
I've finally finished it.
And making incomplete complete
wasn't easy, let me tell you.
It would have been nice if
they'd written the instructions
in words that were a little
easier to understand.
It took a bit of
figuring on my part.
And lots of wracking my
poor little brains out.
The shining wings
that we've claimed,
guided by the seven virtues...
[SHADER sighs]
The Book of
Atonement says
forgiveness for
the fallen angels
will only occur when
the head of Pandemonium,
six of the Apostles, and the
seven virtues are assembled.
Then the drops
of Atonement
will be born in the
great river of souls.
[AION] And Heaven will become
Earth, Earth will become Heaven,
and time will once again
paint a spiral.
The alternate ending
to the Apocalypse
is finally
within our grasp.
And all we need now
is the song of Charity.
That's true, but Chrono
and Mary Magdalene
will be bringing it soon.
Let's have
a welcoming party!
And I'll be in
charge of welcoming.
Joshua still possesses
such incredible power.
[SHADER] I wouldn't have been
able to make this magic circle
if he weren't here.
Please, Lord Aion,
may I take Lord Joshua
back to his quarters now?
All of this has tired him,
and I fear that--
[JOSHUA] No, I'm fine.
Don't worry, Big Sister.
Please, my lord.
You mustn't drain yourself.
[JOSHUA grunts]
Stinking humans.
You sicken me.
Rizel was as good as killed
for this little worm.
What makes him
worth such a price?
[SHADER laughs]
Genai, why are
you so angry?
Please let go of him.
You cannot harm Lord Joshua.
All of you know how vital
his mission is to us.
[GENAI growls]
[GENAI] You human bitch!
Since when have you talked
to your masters like that?
[AION] Behave yourself, Genai.
[laughs]
Feeling pent up, are we?
[coughs]
Thank you for that,
Big Sister.
Why is it always you who ends
up protecting me in the end?
[DUFFAU] I fear that
our time has run out.
In taking the head
of Pandemonium,
Aion has caused
the light of Heaven
to begin to flow
into the darkness.
As the darkness vanishes,
so will the balance
on which Heaven rests,
and this will bring disaster
upon your human world.
Chrono, tell me...
For what purpose is Aion
gathering all the Apostles?
I'm not sure that
I've figured out
what Aion actually has in mind.
He never told me
his true plans,
but he was always saying that
he'd "become the Creator."
And for that he'd
destroy the world?
He's not going
to get the chance.
Huh?
I guess this makes it two
contracts that I'm bound by.
[SATELLA] Don't do it!
Satella?
Seeking help from a devil?
Proposing an
alliance with them?
Just how are you different
from a devil worshipper?
Where has your faith
gone, Rosette?
Right here.
[gasps]
So that's the
mysterious timepiece
I've heard so much of.
[DUFFAU] So, you are
running out of time as well.
It's a price
I'm willing to pay.
Hold on, I'm the one
who's going to settle the
score with Aion, Rosette.
Look, all I know is there's
a battle to be fought.
And if that means I
have to fight, so be it.
And I will fight, sir.
I'll fight with you by my side.
Such noble words.
Truly you are deserving of
the name Mary of Magdalene.
Just what does that mean?
Aion called me
that name as well.
You mean you don't know?
It wasn't just your brother.
You were gifted with a legacy
by the will of Heaven as well.
[ROSETTE] Hm, don't pull my leg.
There's no way that that's true.
I don't have healing
powers like Joshua,
or glowing wings like Azmaria,
or anything like that.
[DUFFAU] Mary,
the Bringer of Light,
as you are called
by the church.
You, whose delicate fate
is about to be
possessed by darkness,
because your true
form has been twisted.
In a short time, marks will
be engraved in your body.
They will protect you
from what is to come.
What marks?
[KATE] Yes, thank you.
We appreciate your assistance,
Reverend Gilliam.
If you can, we would
be most grateful
if you could keep your eye
on Rosette and the others.
[GILLIAM] Oh, I will,
but I must admit,
I was rather impressed
at your willingness
to challenge the will
of the council.
[KATE] I've known it was
going to end up like this
since the day we took
responsibility for Chrono.
[GILLIAM] Yes, but something
about you has changed as well.
Also, concerning Rosette...
Something Duffau
said troubles me.
[SATELLA] Now wait
a second, Rosette.
Are you sure that
you're fine with this?
[ROSETTE]
Perfectly fine.
And let's not forget
what a treasure trove
of information these
devils will be for us.
Information?
About things like your
sister, for instance.
[SATELLA gasps]
[ROSETTE] So we'll be in your
hair for a little while longer.
Oh, and I'd like to
take a bath before bed,
could you take care of
that for me, Steiner?
Yes,
Lady Rosette.
[SATELLA sighs]
Well, in that case,
I'll bill my expenses
to the Magdalenes.
Rosette is so
persistent, isn't she?
That's why I want to
stay by her side forever.
What did you say?
Heh, heh! Nothing.
[ROSETTE sighs]
What did he mean by "marks"?
Ah!
Ahhh!
In a short time, marks will
be engraved in your body.
[ROSETTE yells]
[AZMARIA] Rosette!
Is something wrong?
[ROSETTE] No! It's nothing!
[AZMARIA] Chrono overcame
such a terrible past,
and Rosette made a contract
with a terrifying devil!
I get so intimidated by how
incredible everyone else is.
[SATELLA] But you have the power
of God's Apostles, don't you?
[AZMARIA] Things appear
when I sing, that's all.
Like you, Miss Satella,
you can make things pop
out of jewels, can't you?
[SATELLA] You make it sound like
I'm some kind of
street performer!
[ROSETTE]
Next episode, "Believer."
[AZMARIA] I'm going to sing
more than ever before!