[REMINGTON] They called
it the Roaring Twenties,
but in the shadows of
prosperity, the monsters waited.
To combat this evil,
the exorcist Sister Rosette and
her soul-bound devil, Chrono,
were ordered to
rescue Azmaria,
a young girl associated with
the prophecies of Fatima.
However, while they were able to
briefly steal
the girl to safety,
in the end she was taken back
by Chrono's ancient foe,
Lerajie and his human
master, Ricardo.
[CHRONO] Ah!
[REMINGTON]
Now two questions remain:
What is the source of
Azmaria's power to heal?
And what are Ricardo
and Lerajie's true goals?
[footsteps]
[LERAJIE] Look what I found.
[AZMARIA] Ah!
[AZMARIA screams]
[LERAJIE] Wah!
[LERAJIE] Why... Master?
Who ordered you to set
the ground below us ablaze?
Forget the Sinner!
As long as these chains exist,
you cannot defy me.
And I will have you do no
man's bidding except my own.
Not as long as the contract
between us exists.
Is that understood?
As you wish.
Servant of Fatima,
this is your life's
final stage.
Final?
[RICARDO] This body of mine
lacks the spark of life.
You will bring back that fire.
She's awake!
Are you all right?
Thank goodness.
[ROSETTE] Why are you all...
Where's Chrono?
[REMINGTON]
So, you've come to at last.
[REMINGTON sighs]
I fear that the
foe we now face
is in a different league
from any we have met before.
Chrono.
[ANNA] Rosette, I'm so sorry.
[ROSETTE] What?
I'm afraid that I've
been avoiding you,
since we learned about
Chrono... being a...
We all have.
Me too.
[ROSETTE] No, no, it's all
right. It doesn't bother me.
But, we...
It's fine. Fear is just
a natural response...
to someone who's different.
[ROSETTE winces]
Are you all right, Rosette?
[ANNA] Wait!
You mustn't move yet!
There's no time
to worry about this.
[ROSETTE] Chrono.
[CHRONO] Ah?
[CHRONO] No, you mustn't.
Please.
[ROSETTE] But, Azmaria is...
You saw her...
how she smiled.
Twice! Twice I've failed her.
You're the only one
that can rescue Azmaria!
You're her only hope!
If you called on your powers,
you could heal your
injuries instantly!
You could do it
and save her.
If I use them...
your life will be...
[ROSETTE] I don't care!
We've got to save Azmaria.
There's something
I have to tell her.
Please, Chrono,
I'm begging you!
The source of Chrono's power
is the soul of his contractor.
Rosette...
[RICARDO] You see, my dear,
this body of mine
was blown to bits during
that loathsome war.
--[AZMARIA gasps]
--[RICARDO laughs]
[RICARDO] But it's not
possible for it to die, either.
For I had signed
a pact of undeath
with my contractor, Lerajie.
Thus my physical
body was restored.
But a man is
more than flesh.
Only the corpse itself
was brought back.
While intact,
it is lacking life.
Because of this, I rot!
[RICARDO groans]
I rot because Lerajie's
power has become imperfect.
Once, there was nothing
that he could not do,
but he has since fallen.
My powers were lessened
by the Sinner, Chrono.
Chrono.
And now you will open
the gate to Heaven for us.
A Servant of Fatima, yes,
an Apostle of the most high!
The terms of my contract
must be fulfilled,
no matter what the cost.
And if this imperfect
devil's powers
are inadequate to
the task desired,
then I am forced to use the
power of one who is perfect.
The power of God himself!
[LERAJIE] Let us
begin the ceremony.
Servant of Fatima,
illuminate us with the miracle
the Virgin entrusted to you.
Now, let us hear you sing!
Let us hear you praise God.
[ANNA] Those lights...
what are they?
[ROSETTE] Huh?
They're Astral Lines.
Astral Lines?
Could it be...
...that the power
of the Apostles
comes from the
Astral Lines of Force?
But what are these
Astral Lines?
[REMINGTON] The streams which
compose the Astral Plane,
a great gathering of spiritual
energy that encircles the Earth.
Think of it as a river,
from which all newborn
things are given life,
and to that endless flow, the
souls of the dead must return,
like drops in the river of life.
The source
of all life.
This doesn't make any sense.
What is God trying
to make Azmaria do?
[AZMARIA screams]
[RICARDO] That's it!
Scream even more!
Scream! And scream again!
The Astral power your
voice has summoned
lights the fires of life
in this rotted body.
[screaming continues]
[ANNA]
What do you mean "no"?
I thought that the plane was
supposed to be ready ages ago!
It can't be...
Please, Chrono, help me!
Please.
I don't want Azmaria to
keep suffering like this.
And I know you feel the same
way deep inside. I know it!
[CHRONO] Don't throw your
life away so cheaply.
[ROSETTE] Stop it!
The longer you delay,
the harder it's going to be!
Chrono!
[CHRONO sighs]
[CHRONO]
Ten minutes. No longer.
Thanks, Chrono.
[CHRONO yells]
[gasps]
[AZMARIA]
Ahh! Aaahh!
Huh?
[RICARDO] Lerajie!
That's enough.
[RICARDO] Why have
you stopped it?
Aaahh!
[LERAJIE] Thank you
for all the hard work
you've put into
this plan, Master.
However, I'm afraid that
our intent was never truly
to bring back your life,
as you can see.
A receptor!
[LERAJIE] That's right.
A receptor into which
most of this lovely
Astral energy has gone.
Damn you!
It flows into me,
the Astral radiance,
and with the
blessings of God,
I'm going to break these
chains of yours, Master.
[RICARDO gasps]
Lerajie! Ahh!
[LERAJIE laughs]
[LERAJIE]
And with this, I'm free!
Are you...
Everything's jake, 'kay?
Here we go.
Azmaria!
[LERAJIE grunts]
Lerajie!
What in Hell is he?
[CHRONO] A pursuer.
[ROSETTE] Azmaria!
[LERAJIE] There are so many ways
in which an Apostle can be used.
Neither you nor
Aion shall have her!
[LERAJIE chuckles]
[LERAJIE] You know, Sinner,
I wonder what Aion would think,
seeing you as you
are now, a dog of God.
Aion.
Rosette, you rescue Azmaria.
I'll take care of Lerajie.
[ROSETTE] But what about them?
The only living humans
on this entire ship
are Azmaria and yourself.
What? Then what kind
of creatures are they?
[CHRONO] Legion. Lower class
devils in human form.
[LERAJIE] I'll be claiming your
skull as my prize, Chrono.
And with that trophy, an even
greater rank shall be mine!
Get the Apostle
out of here at once!
[gunfire]
Azmaria...
It's losing altitude!
[CHRONO groans]
[LERAJIE] You're not as
strong as you used to be.
Did becoming God's dog mean
having your fangs pulled?
I didn't have a use for them!
Those eyes! That voice!
Is the shadow that
once struck fear
in the hearts of devils
everywhere vanquished?
What did you lose besides
your rank? What else?
[CHRONO] I think you'll find
that I've gained much more!
[AZMARIA yells]
[ROSETTE] Azmaria, get down!
[ROSETTE exhales]
[AZMARIA] Rosette!
Thank you.
[ROSETTE] Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
[AZMARIA]
What about you, Rosette?
[AZMARIA] Ah.
[AZMARIA] Is that...
really Chrono?
That's right,
Chrono, the Sinner,
the Broken Horn,
the one they cast down.
But whatever name you
choose, he's a devil.
Ah! A devil?
[ROSETTE] Hm.
He doesn't look like one,
but that's because of this.
This special seal restrains
Chrono's power. It has to.
Chrono's powers
feed on the soul...
the life of his contractor.
And every time he
uses his powers,
the shorter the life of
his contractor becomes.
[AZMARIA gasps]
Are you saying that...
[ROSETTE] That's right.
The odds are good that
I won't live to see... thirty.
[AZMARIA] But how?
How could you
sacrifice so much?
How can you do this,
knowing that you'll...
Let me ask you the reverse.
How is it that you can
give up so easily?
[ROSETTE sighs]
I can't understand
that attitude.
"It's bad luck."
"I have no choice."
People who passively
accept their fate...
Because no one knows their
future, least of all me.
So I don't dare
put things off.
I have to do what I can,
while I can still do it.
So, I'll be kicking and
screaming till the very end.
[ROSETTE chuckles]
[CHRONO groans]
[LERAJIE] This is
the power of God!
[LERAJIE laughs]
I gave her my word,
my promise.
[LERAJIE]
To your contractor, hm?
[CHRONO] I have a mission.
And until I make
good that promise,
I'm afraid I can't let you
pursuers take my head!
Wah!
[gasps]
[LERAJIE] Not bad!
Now let me give it back!
[CHRONO] Rah!
Worried about your human?
I can hear the clock tick...
the sounds of her breath.
How many beats does
she have left, Sinner?
[CHRONO yells]
[CHRONO] Rosette!
No! Don't come out here!
[LERAJIE] Allow me to end your
attachments and worries...
forever!
[CHRONO] No!
[CHRONO] Ah!
[LERAJIE laughs]
[LERAJIE] Agh! What was that?
[LERAJIE] Damn you!
[CHRONO] You underestimate
the power of humans.
[LERAJIE] Wah!
[ROSETTE] Azmaria!
[ROSETTE] Ahhh!
[AZMARIA] My wings have always
called forth unhappiness,
but now...
I'll do what I can,
while I can still do it.
[AZMARIA] If I struggle
with all my might...
[AZMARIA] I wonder if something
might begin to change.
[ROSETTE and CHRONO] What?
Your powers...
...don't work anymore?
[AZMARIA] Mm-hmm.
It appears as though I used
my power too much, too quickly.
[ROSETTE] Whoa!
They think it will be a while
before I can recover completely,
a month or two, half a year,
or possibly even longer.
So it appears that there
really is no longer
any reason to keep me here.
Where... should I go now?
[ROSETTE] Listen up!
There's a position open,
in the choir, they say.
The only requirement is that
you have to be older than ten.
With your voice,
we'd be glad to have you.
If it's your choice.
What do you say?
[AZMARIA] Mhmm.
[AZMARIA laughs]
[ROSETTE] This place
is driving me crazy!
The rules are strict,
the food is plain,
we get up at the crack of dawn,
and go to bed too early!
Why can't a girl
have a little fun?
It's too much stress!
[AZMARIA] But that's no reason
to just leave, is it?
[ROSETTE] Oh, the wind of
freedom is calling to me.
[AZMARIA] Rosette!
[CHRONO] Oh, let her go,
she's just being selfish again.
[ROSETTE]
Next episode, "Militia."
[AZMARIA] Yeah! I want to
become just like Rosette!
[CHRONO] Are you okay with that?