Huh?
[ANNA] Ugh.
[ANNA] All right, then.
Huh?
[ANNA screams]
[AION whistles]
Good morning,
great city of Babylon.
This era has turned
out quite nicely.
Don't you agree, my friend?
[gasps]
[REMINGTON] Sister Kate!
The central committee
of the Magdalene Order
has just called for
an emergency meeting.
You must hurry.
I'll take care
of things here.
All right.
I'm counting on you.
Minister, are things
really that bad?
There are still too many
uncertainties right now.
The same thing's been
reported at every church.
In each case, a black sun and
a red moon have been observed.
These omens are
very troubling.
[whispered] A red...
I've seen it, Father.
The red moon.
It's just like before.
All of the signs Aion has come.
[loud clang]
[DRIVER A] What the--?
What? Huh?
[screaming]
[JOSHUA] Ah, the first
angel sounded,
and there followed hail
and fire, mingled with blood,
and they were cast
upon the earth.
And the third part of
trees was burnt up,
and all green
grass was burnt up.
Isn't Aion incredible?
I wanted to see
the red hail, really.
If that's your desire,
then would you like
to go to Manhattan?
Lord Aion did say he would
enjoy having your company
if you wished to come.
Eh, I so hate cities.
The noise of the crowds
is too strong!
Please forgive me, Joshua.
Perhaps I should not
have mentioned it.
It's fine. But why are...
these carrots here?
Vegetables are
healthy for you.
[JOSHUA] Hmm?
Lord Joshua?
[JOSHUA] I smell tainted meat.
[VAGRANT] The sun turned
black like sackcloth
made of goat hair.
The whole moon
turned blood red,
and the stars in
the sky fell to Earth,
as late figs drop
from a fig tree
when shaken by a mighty wind.
The sky receded like a scroll,
rolling up in the heavens.
[VAGRANT yells]
[VAGRANT screams]
[KATE] As you all know
by now, Manhattan,
and especially the area
known as Central Park,
is an important focus for
supernatural occurrences.
The predecessors of the
Magdalene Order discovered
that this place was connected
to the limbo of Pandemonium.
For that reason, they
erected a seal to act
as a protective boundary.
We believe that the
current outbreak of living dead
appearing across the city
is the result of that
seal being breached.
The purpose of the red hail
that fell this morning
was to break the seal.
[COUNCIL LEADER] Sister Kate,
you are to act with
all possible speed
in restoring the Seal
of the Seven Wings.
[KATE] I understand, senior.
[AZMARIA] Wait, Rosette!
[ROSETTE] What?
[AZMARIA] Wait. I'm going too.
You don't know how
frightening Aion is, Azmaria.
That's right. And you know
Aion wants the Apostles.
You already know that
Aion took my brother Joshua
simply because he's an Apostle.
Our job is to protect
you from him.
Well maybe I'm tired of being
protected all of the time.
I want to fight for myself!
[ROSETTE and CHRONO] Uhh...
Get in.
[REMINGTON] The spiritual
blockade is now complete.
All that's left is to
seal off the miasma.
We're going to restore
the Seal of the Seven Wings.
All of you, go to your
assigned positions.
Once you have completed
your tasks, you will contact me.
But sir, Rosette
still isn't here.
Oh, that girl.
How can she be
late for this?
[REMINGTON sighs]
[REMINGTON] Everyone else,
do your duty!
[MILITIA] Yes, sir!
I'm so sorry we're late, sir!
[AZMARIA] Rosette!
Wait! If you get covered
in that, you'll die!
[REMINGTON] I'm afraid
it's as Chrono says.
The miasma is evil,
accumulated in Pandemonium
which now has physical form.
Evil that's claimed
a number of victims today.
Evil? But what kind?
From human hearts.
From hearts?
Ones filled with greed. Evil.
Spiritual decay
is the very stuff
on which the devil world feeds.
That's so disgusting.
You mean something horrible like
that is really under Manhattan?
[REMINGTON]
We say "below,"
but we don't mean that
it's literally there.
Now please hurry
to your positions.
[ROSETTE] Understood, sir.
[CHRONO] Here you go.
You use these just
like you would use
the Principatus class,
understand?
[AZMARIA] Right.
Get that barrier up
right now, you two!
[CHRONO and AZMARIA] Right!
It's just one after another.
I'm finished.
[CHRONO] All right.
Just one more!
Right.
--[CHRONO] Here you go.
--[AZMARIA] Thanks.
[CHRONO] Come on, hurry.
[AZMARIA] Right!
[AZMARIA screams]
--[CHRONO] Rosette!
--[ROSETTE] Chrono!
[SATELLA] Kommen sie.
I command you, take form now!
Bring forth jewel drop!
Rain down,
like a thunderstorm!
Tear the ground asunder!
My clear February!
[REMINGTON] Hmm.
Guten Tag.
In trouble again?
Satella. Why are you here?
The New York Police have
retained my services.
Perhaps someone doesn't
completely trust your order
to do the job.
Shut up, you pill.
The New York Police aren't
exactly known for integrity.
Such sour grapes.
Just hurry up and
put up that barrier.
It's outside my area
of expertise, after all.
Grr. I know that!
Chrono! Azmaria! Back to work!
Him!
What?
He's here. Now.
This feeling...
A devil!
[AION chuckles]
Who, me?
I am the Alpha and Omega.
The beginning and the end.
The start and the finish.
Aion!
Aion?
[AION chuckles]
You know, I had thought you'd be
able to tell that I was coming.
Kommen sie. Reveal
your form, juwel ritter.
Satella, no!
He's not a normal--
Devil! All of whom
must be destroyed!
[SATELLA] Ah!
[SATELLA] Huh?
[AION] My, my. What an admirable
thing you just did, Chrono.
[CHRONO groans]
Chrono!
[AION] Where is the
Chrono who was trying
to help me change Pandemonium?
Come back.
Let's work together again.
This world of humans
isn't so bad, is it?
And we can live here,
because these people,
this nation, this whole world
has welcomed us,
through greed and avarice.
It's ours for the asking.
Sorry. I'm not like you.
[AION] I see.
[CHRONO yells]
[ROSETTE] Ah! Chrono!
Ah, dear Rosette Christopher.
You've grown into such
a lovely young lady.
Where's Joshua?
[AION] If I don't answer,
will you shoot me?
Who else knows where
your sweet Joshua might be?
[CHRONO groans]
[weakly] Rosette.
Heh. Predictable...
Mary Magdalene.
But that's enough.
I'm here for someone else.
Come on out,
little Apostle girl.
The disasters that
have occurred today
are my way of welcoming
you into the fold.
[MILITIA A] Group three,
barrier preparations complete.
[MILITIA B]
Group five, complete.
[MILITIA C] This is group six.
Preparations are complete.
That's understood.
All groups, stand by and
maintain your positions.
[gunfire]
[CLAIRE] Sir, we still
haven't heard from Rosette.
[ANNA] What is that girl doing?
Don't get distracted, you two!
[REMINGTON] Rosette...
It couldn't be.
[AION] Rosette,
you're so, so mistaken.
The truth is that my
actions saved Joshua.
Saved him?
Don't listen, Rosette!
[AION] Listen, you who
wishes to kill all devils.
Listen, my dear
little Apostle girl.
[AZMARIA gasps]
[AION] The truth is
that this is His fault!
All of those tragedies
that happened to you,
all of the horrors
that made you stumble,
were nothing more than traps,
set by the being
you call your "God."
Tell me,
Rosette Christopher,
have you heard
his voice even once?
Rosette! You mustn't listen!
[CHRONO] No!
[ROSETTE] Chrono!
Don't kill him!
If he dies, I'll never
find my younger brother!
There's no way a devil's
going to help you!
[ROSETTE] Please...
Please, Satella.
[AION laughs]
Isn't this fun?
Even at a time like this,
the one you worship won't speak
one little word to save you.
Believe me, this is
your world as it is.
He doesn't see anything.
He doesn't save anyone.
You understand this,
don't you, Apostle girl?
This, while you were cursed
with his so called blessing.
The curse that you
carried every day.
Such hypocrisy and deception.
He's naught but
a minor villain,
oozing honeyed words
and destruction,
grown arrogant from His
own inflated ego, your God.
And what about you,
our young Apostle girl?
Your search for a place
where you could be at peace.
How long and difficult
has your path been?
And then there's you,
jewel witch.
Ten years spent searching
for the family that you lost,
without any clues.
It must have been painful.
But I can save you all from
the curse of the Almighty God.
Don't you see?
It was from this
that I saved Joshua.
[ROSETTE] Stop saying
that, you bastard!
[AION] You're pointing that
gun at the wrong person.
The one you need to
defeat is in Heaven.
Of course, creatures such as
yourselves cannot defeat Him.
But I can. Right, Chrono?
Isn't that the reason
why we accepted
being branded as Sinners?
[CHRONO yells]
[ROSETTE] Chrono!
[gasps]
We should work... together.
Apostle, for this purpose,
I need your power...
Azmaria Hendric.
Let me save you, my child.
[ROSETTE yells]
[AION chuckles]
[AION] Desist. You're not going
to shoot, and you know it.
[ROSETTE screams]
[gunshot]
I won't let you have Azmaria!
But you gave me
your brother.
[AION] Oh, poor, poor
Rosette Christopher.
But I can save even you.
Rosette!
[AION] Give yourself over
to me, Mary of Magdalene.
Rosette, no!
[CHRONO] Get away from her!
The miasma!
[REMINGTON] Huh?
--[CHRONO yells]
--[SATELLA] Chrono!
That's right!
It's time for you to spread
your Sinner's wings, Chrono!
Aion!
[AZMARIA] Chrono, no!
[CHRONO yells]
Stop doing this!
Please stop!
[whispered] Azmaria...
[AZMARIA] I'll come with you.
Please, please
don't hurt my friends.
I'm begging you.
[AION] Just what I would
have expected from someone
who received God's blessing
as the Apostle of Charity.
No! Don't!
Doing this won't make
anything better, Azmaria.
[AION] Come with me... Apostle.
[AION] Gah!
[REMINGTON] Seal it!
[SATELLA] Azmaria!
He's gone.
But will he be back?
Yeah. It's just started.
That thing that we defeated
wasn't the real Aion.
[AION] So, that's what
happens with a Shadow?
But for you to take the trouble
of sending out your Holy Mother.
A sly move indeed.
Perhaps a change
of strategy then.
Chrono, I'll leave that
Apostle with you for now.
[KATE] The restoration of
the barrier was successful.
But there is a much
bigger problem.
The secret plans of the
Sinners and their allies.
[COUNCIL LEADER]
There is also the matter
of the sealed third prophecy.
We must carefully fathom
what the Lord's intentions are.
[FIORE] That's right.
He's had another fit.
[JOSHUA] I'm looking
forward to it, Fi.
I want to meet
the others soon.
The other Apostles.
[FIORE] It appears that
I am not good enough.
I really think his real
older sister might be...
[ROSETTE laughs]
[ROSETTE] Oh, my gosh!
Father Remington asked
me out on a date!
[CHRONO] Oh.
[REMINGTON] Um, Rosette,
we've all been rather busy
with these cases, haven't we?
Perhaps we should spend a little
time talking about our future.
[ROSETTE] And just like that,
the two of us will board a train
and go away together.
[ROSETTE] Just kidding.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
[CHRONO] The weather report
says it's gonna rain tomorrow.
[REMINGTON]
Next episode, "Puppet."
[ROSETTE] What?
You're giving me a doll?
[ROSETTE] What do you
think I am, a kid?