Hurry! Hurry!
We're gonna be late!
You're the one who had
to take a nap, remember?
[AZMARIA] Oh, Rosette, I--
[ROSETTE] Sorry, Azmaria!
We're in a rush,
no time for chit-chat!
[AZMARIA] Oh...
[ROSETTE pants]
[ROSETTE] S-Sorry for being
late, I brought Chrono with me!
[KATE] It's the first time a
devil has entered this room.
[ROSETTE laughs]
I assume you know the
reason that you're here.
Did you find
anything indicating
a connection between
Lerajie's recent actions...
...and those of Aion?
No, ma'am. We think this
was just Lerajie's scheme.
From what we can tell,
he was only planning
to absorb the Astral Lines in
order to revive his own power.
Is that so?
Rosette, I apologize if this has
brought up some
painful memories.
As if I could ever
forget what happened!
Not when Aion's the devil
who took my brother,
Joshua, from me!
I could never forget!
[REMINGTON] Thanks to Azmaria,
we now understand the
role of the Apostles.
If they are able to
summon the Astral Lines,
then the reason for which Aion
took Joshua is now clear.
He's seeking a way to
acquire the power of God.
But if he's trying
to do that, sir,
what do you think
Aion's real goal is?
[KATE] We think he's planning
a war against Heaven.
And that which drives him,
is not Satan's plan,
but a desire to
remake the universe
to his own warped vision.
I fear that's the only
conclusion that makes sense.
You should also know this:
For Aion's war to succeed,
it will be necessary for him to
possess both Joshua and Azmaria.
[ROSETTE gasps]
In the time before we
were called the Sinners,
there was something
that Aion used to say--
that the only thing one born
imperfect should strive for
is to become perfect.
He swore to create his
own end of the world...
To make his own apocalypse.
[ROSETTE]
Another end of the world?
He'll destroy the destinies
of Joshua and everyone else,
just to play God!
The only reason I came here was
to get help finding my brother.
And from what I've seen,
I'm ready to give those
monsters a decent fight!
Rosette!
Please, Sister!
Please assign me the mission
of finding the Apostles!
I swear I won't let you down!
I've told you that's
still under inquiry!
Besides, what could you
possibly do on your own?
We're talking about my
little brother, dammit!
[KATE] Enough!
You're too emotionally
involved in this right now.
If you can't
control yourself,
someday you won't even see
what's right in front of you!
You're part of this Order!
You can't afford to forget
the rules that we operate by!
[ROSETTE] But--
[KATE] If you must know,
Father Remington has been asked
to investigate the
whereabouts of the Apostles,
beginning with Joshua.
In the meantime, I'll be
placing you on common duty,
so you have time to cool off
that hot head of yours!
[ROSETTE] Jeez! Why is she
always so hard-headed?
And why'd she have
to be like that?
She never
understands anything!
[CHRONO] Wait for me, Rosette!
[ROSETTE]
Get a wiggle on, slowpoke.
[AZMARIA] Oh! Um, Rosette!
Oh, Azmaria,
sorry about that!
Silly me!
[ROSETTE laughs]
[AZMARIA chuckles]
[AZMARIA] You two
are always so busy.
[ROSETTE] Well, yeah,
that's because there are
always devils causing
trouble someplace.
[CHRONO] So, um,
how's the choir?
Oh, I'm really
enjoying it!
And in our next recital,
I'll have a solo!
It's good to see
you smiling, now.
You really had the two
of us worried for a bit.
Well, everything's
changed for the better.
[ROSETTE] That's funny,
I've changed a lot
since I came here, too.
And I've learned a lot
of different things.
I've grown up a lot,
and this place has kinda
been like a school.
Hm.
But now there's nothing
left for me to learn here!
--[CHRONO] Huh?
--It's time! To leave!
[CHRONO and AZMARIA] Huh?
Didn't Sister Kate
say that I'd end up
not even seeing what's in front
of me if things don't change?
If I stay here,
I'll go blind!
I don't think that's
what she meant!
[ROSETTE] There's no use
trying to stop me,
I'm going to find
Joshua on my own.
Wa, ha, ha! Ha, ha, ha!
Ahhhh!
[thud]
Ow!
Um, are you all right, Rosette?
Chrono, we're going!
What, right now?
[ROSETTE] Of course, right now!
There's no time like the present
when there's a job to be done!
So, I'm getting gone
as fast as I can!
I think this is a
bad idea, Rosette.
It's fine! I've decided,
and that's that.
[REMINGTON]
And what did you decide?
[ROSETTE] Huh?
Wah! Fa-Fa-Fa-Fa-
Fa-Father Remington!
I thought you
might come here.
I-I'm really sorry,
Father, sir.
But I just want to
find my brother, Joshua!
Have you considered
joining the militia?
[ROSETTE] Huh? The militia?
The First Class?
Yes. As you no doubt know,
that class have been
granted certain privileges,
including the right to conduct
their own investigations.
In fact, several militia
have been investigating
their own private cases
for quite some time.
That would be a perfect
fit for you right now.
But, how could I...
Sister Kate must be convinced
of your own ability to fight...
at that level.
I get it.
Show her my abilities!
[CHRONO] Uhh...
Well, what's your beef?!
Uh, nothing at all!
[KATE] Here you are. I added an
extra helping of milk and sugar.
[AZMARIA] Um, thanks.
This is good!
Isn't it? It's a special
blend of black tea leaves
I received as a gift!
Now then, what did you want?
And... you won't laugh?
Of course not.
Listening to the problems
of others is part of our work.
Even if what I want is to
become more like Rosette?
[KATE coughs]
I want to become a
distinguished exorcist like her
and devote the rest of my life
to helping people in trouble!
Is that so strange?
[KATE] Well, I'm afraid
that allowing someone
to follow her lead is...
[AZMARIA] I hated it...
this power.
I even hated myself,
and how I made the people
around me unhappy.
But...
Rosette never, ever gave up.
And I... never want
to give up again!
I want to do things for
others just like she does!
Azmaria...
[footsteps]
It's cold because
the room's temperature
is regulated to maintain
the spirit energy.
This is where Rosette did
all of her training as well.
Oh, my!
[KATE] It was invented
by the Elder,
to project energy
formation fields,
and uses mock spirit form
containment units.
To put it simply, this is
our exorcist training area.
The targets are
artificial poltergeists.
By using this system,
we can simulate indoor
and outdoor battles
with all kinds of monsters,
under any conditions.
Real monsters?
[KATE chuckles]
Oh, relax, my dear.
The spirit energy is controlled
for training purposes.
We won't make a novice
deal with too much.
Now, just go down these
stairs and wait, child.
I'll give you more
detailed instructions
from the control room.
[AZMARIA] Right.
[CHRONO] Do you remember...
when you and I first came here?
[door opens]
[REMINGTON] Have you
prepared yourself?
[ROSETTE] Yes, sir.
Incidentally, Chrono's
staying here with me.
[CHRONO] Huh?
It's "why," not "huh."
If you were to go with her,
it wouldn't be much
of a test, would it?
Now, Rosette, would
you please hand over
that little watch of yours?
[ROSETTE] So,
where's Sister Kate?
She'll be informed later.
She'll be informed later?
If we get the right results,
I'll find a way to explain
it to her afterwards.
[ROSETTE] Oh.
[REMINGTON chuckles]
[REMINGTON] Are you ready
to start, Rosette?
[ROSETTE] Yes, you can
start whenever you want!
[REMINGTON]
Level twenty's the one used
by the most advanced class.
[CHRONO] Right, Father.
Initiate spiritual
energy field.
[AZMARIA] Huh?
[REMINGTON] Release the targets!
[CHRONO] Right.
[REMINGTON] Beginning recording.
The condition for
passing this test
is the extermination of
all targets within one hour.
[REMINGTON] Very well,
then. Good luck.
[ROSETTE] Yes, sir!
[CHRONO gasps]
I sense something evil!
[REMINGTON] Oh, yes, that.
Actually, I released
a real monster down there.
It was one of the
most powerful spirits
we had sealed in storage.
What?! But why?!
She has to see what
she's really up against.
If she can't clear her way
through a simple
problem like this,
she won't ever be able
to convince Sister Kate.
[KATE] What was
that you just said?
Gah!
Huh? Ah.
What is going on here!?
[AZMARIA] Sister Kate?
Where are you?
[AZMARIA] Ah!
[INSTRUCTOR] You're too slow!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
[AZMARIA] Huh?
[AZMARIA] Uh...
[AZMARIA screams]
[REMINGTON]
It's natural to be scared.
Your opponents are
monsters, after all.
But the important
thing comes after that.
Taking one step forward,
no matter how
frightened you are.
[REMINGTON] Rosette,
can you hear me?
Yes.
There's been an accident.
I'm sorry, but we
must stop the test.
[ROSETTE] What? Why?
Tell me the reason!
Azmaria is down there,
and we can't contact her.
What? Azmaria!
[REMINGTON] And, there's a real
devil on the loose down there.
What, but how?
Well, I released it,
in order to test your strength.
But I never thought there would
be someone there before you.
What did you just say?!
You shouldn't have been
here in the first place!
[ROSETTE] Gah! Sister Kate!
[KATE] Rosette,
come back right now.
We'll take care of
the rest of this,
do you understand me?
What about Azmaria?
She'll be all right.
We'll rescue her right now,
so don't worry.
Is that understood, Rosette?
[ROSETTE] Father Remington.
[REMINGTON] Huh?
[ROSETTE] Please, sir,
I'm begging you,
give me permission to go
and rescue Azmaria.
Are you out of your mind?!
Please, Rosette, we're dealing
with a Mind Eater, here.
It possesses you, reads your
mind, and then impersonates you.
This particular one was
responsible for over
fifty murders during
the Civil War.
This isn't something
you can handle, Rosette.
Let the militia deal with this!
[ROSETTE] But ma'am...
--[static]
--Huh? Rosette! Rosette!
Answer us, Rosette!
Is something wrong?
[ROSETTE] Father?
Father Remington?
[distant laughter]
[ROSETTE yells]
Don't scare me
like that, Azmaria!
[laughter]
Rosette!
[ROSETTE groans]
[laughter]
This body possesses power!
Wonderful power!
[ROSETTE] Azmaria!
Get a hold of yourself!
Azmaria! Azmaria!
[MIND EATER screams]
I gotta help Rosette!
[REMINGTON] Wait!
Wait for what, Father?
We can't just stand
here and watch them die!
[REMINGTON] This is the moment
of truth for Rosette.
You don't mean--
Do you know
what you're saying?
That thing down there is going
to eat their hearts and souls!
If you were to save her now,
nothing is gained at all.
And under these circumstances,
she has only one option left.
You want Rosette to perform
a soul exorcism... alone?
[KATE] Your little test could
cost Rosette dearly.
[REMINGTON] Yet not
everything can be solved
by pulling the trigger of a gun.
But if there's trouble,
then I'm going in.
All we can do now is pray.
Pray that Azmaria's causality
won't overtly influence Rosette.
Causality...
Of course, honestly,
I'm not very good at diving.
Here I go!
Azmaria! Look over
here, Azmaria!
If you don't fight back,
your soul is going
to be taken over!
[MIND EATER] It's no use.
You're the Mind Eater.
That child... will
never move again.
Do you see those
graves there?
Her mother and father's,
the orchestra members
that cared for her...
her powers were the
cause of all their deaths.
God has entrusted
her with a great power,
yet her heart
fears any use of it.
Azmaria.
[KATE] Those entrusted
with the power of God,
are always burdened
with the cross
of an equally great causality.
[REMINGTON] Not unlike our Lord.
They are considered
macabre by the ignorant,
and when they finally find
peace, it is all taken away.
[MIND EATER] I can hear her,
"If only I didn't
have this power..."
Joshua.
[MIND EATER]
Loneliness, fear, anxiety,
and, more than
anything else, power.
Quite a comfortable
place. Oh yes.
Shut up, you fiend. I came
here to rescue Azmaria,
not listen to you!
[AZMARIA] Huh?
[ROSETTE] What? What is this?
Azmaria, can you hear me?
There's nothing wrong
with being afraid!
But keeping those fears to
yourself won't solve anything!
[MIND EATER] Keep your
mouth shut, nasty girl.
[ROSETTE grunts]
Listen, Azmaria, you don't have
to be afraid of your power!
You have to fight back!
You're not alone in this world!
I'm here for you!
Chrono is too!
We'll be by your side!
[AZMARIA gasps]
[MIND EATER] Shut up!
The important thing is...
even when you're
scared, taking it in stride,
and taking a step
forward anyways.
[ROSETTE screams]
Rosette!
[AZMARIA] No!
Don't take Rosette away!
[CHRONO]
Rosette! Rosette!
[ROSETTE] Chrono...?
Jeepers, I can't believe you
actually fought with causality.
[ROSETTE] Chrono,
where's Azmaria?
[CHRONO chuckles]
Azmaria!
Thank you, Rosette.
Thank you.
[AZMARIA giggles]
[AZMARIA] Rosette,
I saw something.
[ROSETTE] Yeah, I saw it too.
[AZMARIA] Chrono, you're
completely different from
what I thought a devil
would be like, aren't you?
[CHRONO] Yeah, I get that a lot.
[AZMARIA] You always do what
Rosette tells you to do,
you get involved in
difficult situations,
and you burden yourself
with other people's troubles.
You don't seem
like a devil at all.
[CHRONO] Yeah,
I get that a lot, too.
[AZMARIA] I love you for
being that way, Chrono!
[SATELLA] Next episode,
"Jewel Witch."
[CHRONO] Hold on!
[AZMARIA] Who was that?