[FIORE] Lord Joshua?
Huh?
Lord Joshua?!
[JOSHUA] Ah!
[FIORE] Lord Josh--
[JOSHUA groans]
[FIORE] Joshua...
Sister? The noise is horrible.
If I don't drown it out
like this... I...
There's nothing to worry
about, Lord Joshua.
Please, let me take
you back to your bed.
[JOSHUA whimpers]
I'm sorry, but if you stay like
this, you'll catch a cold.
[JOSHUA] Leave it on!
[JOSHUA] Again... the noise
keeps coming back...
Again and again...
And it's getting worse.
I can feel it in my head!
[AION] So, it's no good unless
it's his real sister after all.
[FIORE] Lady Rizel has
already gone to get her.
Has she now?
She said it was...
unseemly, sir.
[train whistle blows]
[ROSETTE] Only seventy hours
'til we reach San Francisco.
Compared to the last
four years, that's nothing.
If I just sit still,
this train will take me
to where Joshua is.
[CHRONO] Rosette?
Sorry, did I wake you?
Unh-uh.
Can't you sleep?
Not really. I've never been
very good at staying still.
You can't relax unless you're
destroying something, eh?
[ROSETTE] Hey, just what are
you implying I am, you heel?
Nothing, just that this is
how you need to be, Rosette.
[AZMARIA murmurs]
[CHRONO] Shh!
[train whistle blows]
[bells ring]
[MARY] I keep wondering...
how Rosette and the others
are doing right now.
[CLAIRE] It's Azmaria
I worry about the most.
Do you think she'll be
all right, Sister Kate?
But what if she gets attacked
by monsters or something?!
Don't be so obtuse!
Rosette and Chrono are
out there with her!
[KATE chuckles]
That much is true.
However, let's say a
special prayer for them.
Now that they have
gathered their courage
and gone to face the
destiny that awaits them.
[AZMARIA] Hmm...
What's with that smile?
Judging from the
look on your face,
you must have had
some wonderful dreams.
Not quite, but
when I woke up,
both of you were
there beside me,
and I guess that
just made me feel
really happy for some reason.
[ROSETTE] Huh?
So I'm happy... because
I know this isn't a dream.
You see?
And yet the truth is
that I'm actually
leading you into danger.
[AZMARIA] Huh?
[ROSETTE] And I'm wondering
if it's really for the best.
But this is what I wanted!
I don't want you
worrying about it!
And finding the
Sinners will be...
lots easier if
I'm around, right?
You know, you're
one tough kid.
[AZMARIA giggles]
[door opens]
[JIMMY] Oh, banana oil!
Oh my, it's so crowded.
What a bother.
[JIMMY] I wanna sit, Mama.
Um, you can sit over
here if you'd like.
[MOTHER] Oh my,
I'm so sorry, Sister.
Are you quite sure?
Sure! We can switch out and
take turns sitting, okay?
Chrono, move those bags.
Right.
You're all so terribly kind.
Well, say thank you, Jimmy.
Thank you, thank you, sir!
Oh, you're welc-- [gasps]
[CHRONO] This feeling...
As if something or
someone was watching me.
Could this boy be...
[WOMAN] Ahem, could you
please clear the aisle?
[CHRONO] Eh?
[ROSETTE and CHRONO]
Satella!
You Magdalenes!
You have no idea how to
behave in public, do you?
[CHRONO] Ah, so that's what it--
[ROSETTE] Now wait a second!
What are you doing here?!
Working, of course.
I have an assignment
out on the west coast.
On the other hand,
why are you here?
Is this the freight car?
[ROSETTE grunts angrily]
[train whistle blows]
Come on, Jimmy!
You and your Mama can
come inside now, it's fine.
It seems that a
certain rich lady
who doesn't know how to
behave in proper society,
rented an entire car.
There's really lots of room!
But I don't think...
Oh no, go right ahead.
After all, with
this many rooms,
there's no way she
could use them all.
Isn't that right, Princess?
Do as you wish.
But I could have sworn that
when you rented a train,
you rented the entirety
of it at once.
[ROSETTE] Oh, you're
just so infuriating!
Oh my goodness.
Um, Sister. I know
it's not very much,
but perhaps you'd like to share
these with all of your friends!
Oh, thank you so very much!
[SATELLA] I swear, the way
you reverse emotionally
over food has to be some
kind of paranormal talent.
[ROSETTE] Hmph! Well,
I know a certain jewel witch
who's not getting any then.
Ooh, they're muffins!
[gasps]
[MOTHER] My dear Sister Rosette,
I have something very
urgent to discuss with you.
Meet me in the
cafeteria immediately.
However, you must come alone.
[ROSETTE] Uh... Hey, wait!
[CHRONO] Huh?
It wouldn't be right
for us to eat
all these muffins by ourselves.
I think I'll go and
give Jimmy one.
[CHRONO] Eh?
Uh, well, you know, a treat
always tastes better
when you share it
with someone else.
I'm going back for just
a little bit, okay?
But Rosette!
All right, you. I want
to know who you are!
Huh?
[chattering]
Just who in the hell are you?
And why do you have
Joshua's picture?
[OLD MAN] You should
calm that temper...
...dear Sister Rosette.
[MAN A] But how good
of you to come at last.
[WOMAN] We've been waiting
for you for so long.
You're the one from before.
It's been a while since
we met, dear Sister.
But I've come back for
you... as promised.
[train whistle blows]
A-A-Ahhh!
[CHRONO] Azmaria!
Did you fall again?
You do that a lot, don't you?
[AZMARIA] I'm sorry, ma'am.
I guess I'm just worried about
Rosette and can't concentrate.
She's probably stopped by
the dining car or something.
That girl eats like
a horse, after all.
[ROSETTE] I know all
about your perversions.
So what do you want?
[MOTHER] Please,
there's no need to rush.
Let's be friendly about this.
[ROSETTE] And why
would I want to?
[MOTHER] Perhaps because you
want to see Lord Joshua.
Lord Joshua? Are you
saying my brother's all right?
Yes. Quite well, considering.
Although he says the
noise bothers him.
The noise?
He's... not in pain, is he?
Well he's always screaming.
And to be honest, I wish that
he'd just go elsewhere.
But no one asks me.
And why Lord Aion
is so fixated
on that one is
something I'll never...
[ROSETTE] What's with her?
Why is she so...
[MOTHER] But back to business.
I'll be changing
your travel plans now.
[explosion]
[ROSETTE] Ah!
[train whistle blows]
[MOTHER] I'm afraid that
leaving your friends behind
was quite necessary.
After all, it would be
rather inexcusable
to bring Chrono
before Lord Aion.
[laughter]
[MOTHER] But since your precious
Lord Joshua is calling for you,
even from the depths
of his suffering...
Perhaps seeing you
will comfort him.
Or, if you're so inclined,
you could even end it all
with your precious gun.
[MOTHER laughs]
[ROSETTE] Damn you!
[MOTHER] Ah!
I want you to stop
the train right now,
and set the passengers free!
Do it now!
Please, Sister Rosette,
forgive me.
And forgive my son.
[RIZEL laughs]
[RIZEL] Are you going
to shoot her, Sister...
this innocent
little marionette?
She's just a
human in my web.
J-Jimmy!
[MOTHER sobs]
[RIZEL laughs]
[RIZEL] Oh that face! I so
wanted to see that face!
What can you do?
What shall we
do next for fun?
What with this lovely Sister?
[MOTHER laughs]
Aaahhh!
A barrier!
Ahh!
Chrono!
Heh. I thought that muffin
guff was suspicious.
When it comes to lying,
you're no Barrymore, Rosette.
Ha, hah!
Thanks, Chrono, I owe you!
Uh, Rosette!
Where'd the Life Pod go?
[ROSETTE gasps]
[RIZEL laughs]
[RIZEL] So you finally noticed.
I found myself such a lovely
new toy to play with.
[CHRONO] She's in first class!
[ROSETTE] Satella! Azmaria!
I'm sorry, Rosette.
Satella was trying
to protect me.
Where are you?!
[RIZEL laughs]
[RIZEL] How many times
do I have to remind you?
My puppets are still humans.
But if you want to
shoot so badly...
[TRAIN MAN] Stand over there.
Enough talk!
Ahh!
Okay!
[whispering] Please, Rosette.
Let's just do as they say.
[AZMARIA whimpers]
[RIZEL laughs]
[TRAIN MAN] And now... you...
Shoot him.
[ROSETTE gasps]
No, Rosette!
[RIZEL laughs]
[RIZEL] Hurry up and fire,
Sister Rosette!
Just do it!
Go ahead and shoot me!
No, Chrono! You can't!
Rosette, aim right here.
And don't miss. The center.
[AZMARIA] No, Rosette!
You can't shoot Chrono!
[ROSETTE]
Azmaria, please Azmaria.
I need you to pray
for Chrono for me.
[AZMARIA yells]
[ROSETTE] Chrono!
Chrono?
[ROSETTE] Excuse me!
Until we get back,
please don't leave this car.
No matter what happens!
Oh, and Satella, try not to
get knocked out this time!
[SATELLA] What?
What did you say?
[CHRONO] Okay, okay,
that's enough, you two.
[MOTHER chuckles]
[door opens]
[ROSETTE] Here we go.
Watch your backs.
There!
[ROSETTE gasps]
[ROSETTE yells]
[CHRONO] Rosette!
[RIZEL laughs]
[RIZEL] So we finally
meet, Big Sister.
It's not what I'd planned,
but as long as I bring you back
it should be satisfactory.
Chrono!
[RIZEL] And now that
those nuisances are gone,
our real journey
can begin at last!
[ROSETTE]
What about the engineers?
Release your hostages first!
[RIZEL laughs]
[RIZEL] Don't be ridiculous!
There aren't any
hostages on this train.
I ate them all.
[ROSETTE gasps]
Ahhh!
Ahhh! Damn you!
[RIZEL laughs]
[RIZEL] Sorry, Sister. Now that
you're in my web, I have you.
Come quietly and Lord Aion
will be most pleased.
[ROSETTE] There she
goes about Aion again.
[RIZEL laughs]
[RIZEL] Poor little fly,
alone you have no hope.
But I'm not alone!
[RIZEL] Hmm?
Because I know that
Chrono's all right.
I've always been
able to sense him.
And because of that,
we're never alone!
[RIZEL] Mm. Still trying
to act tough, are you?
[ROSETTE] I'm just
telling the truth, Rizel.
I believe in Chrono.
You're the one...
who's really alone!
Aahh!
[ROSETTE screams]
[RIZEL laughs]
[RIZEL] That's quite a nice
look for you, Sister.
So... comely.
Too bad we can't show
it to your friends.
Little fool!
I told you,
resistance is pointless!
[gun clicks]
[RIZEL] No bullets?
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
What wonderful timing.
If I don't end it
here and now,
Lord Aion would
probably scold me.
[ROSETTE]
Aion this! Aion that!
You're such a dumb dora.
You know how important
he thinks Joshua is.
And yet you're not worth
a second of his time.
That's why you're so
desperate to bring me...
So he'll notice you.
You know nothing about it!
You're such a pathetic sap.
There's no one who cares
about you, not even Aion!
Be silent!
Just try and make me!
[train whistle blows]
[ROSETTE] No one loves you,
you monster.
[RIZEL] Shut up!
[ROSETTE] It's tough,
isn't it? And it hurts.
[RIZEL] Silence!
[ROSETTE] And no matter
how much you love him,
he'll never notice you, never!
Don't worry. God will
have pity... even on you!
Shut up you little bitch!
[ROSETTE]
I'll pray for you, Rizel.
Oh Lord, please
save this mad woman
from her unrequited love!
[RIZEL screams]
[ROSETTE yells]
[gunshot]
[RIZEL screams]
Ahhhh!
Go up! Geh aufwaerts!
Chrono...
[CHRONO chuckles]
[loud thud]
I'm going to kill you!
I'll rip out your organs!
I'll drain your blood dry!
[RIZEL screams]
Lord Aion, I failed.
[train whistle blows]
Alas, poor Rizel.
And it all
came to naught.
[CHRONO] We're destined
to get into trouble
no matter where
we go, aren't we?
[ROSETTE] It's just what
happens, you know?
[CHRONO] I was really looking
forward to riding on the train,
but with a pile of scrap
metal for an engine...
[ROSETTE] You're a devil,
so stop harping, okay?
We're in San Francisco.
[CHRONO] I hope they plan on
building some new bridges.
I'd better go see them
before they're gone!
[ROSETTE]
Next episode, "Prayer."
[CHRONO] Please let us end this
without destroying
anything else.