[REMINGTON]
The roaring twenties.
An age of gold...
A time when great evils
still walked the night,
hidden in the shroud
of darkness.
A time when a new
continent reveled
in the spring after
the last war,
ready to achieve an
age of unprecedented
economic development.
But that which moves men
moves other things as well.
And when change
comes too quickly,
the inhuman things that
writhe beneath the earth
may be drawn to the surface
from the abysmal depths.
[JOSHUA] Ah...
[JOSHUA gasps]
Who are you?
First tell us who
and what you are.
My name is Chrono.
And what I am is what
your people call a devil.
What do you mean
by a "devil"?
Just what I said.
One of the beings
that you humans fear.
[CHRONO yelps]
[ROSETTE] Sir,
are you all right?
You're looking awful weak.
You should eat something.
Here! Help yourself!
[CHRONO] Huh?
Um, thank you?
My name is Rosette,
and my brother is Joshua.
This is great!
Could... Could I shake
your hand? Please?
[CHRONO] Uh...
You're really... a devil?
Wow! A devil!
This is so swell.
Aion!
Joshua, no! Stay away!
[ROSETTE] Ah!
Joshua...
--Hey, Rosette.
--Huh?
Just how do you
feel about Chrono?
[ROSETTE] Huh?
Well, you are
always together.
And get this, Claire was
saying that she wants to
work with Chrono, too.
Oh, Anna, Anna.
All I said was that I thought he
was very nice, and that's all.
So, how do you
really feel?
How do...? It's not
an easy thing to...
Oh! You don't mean
you think that...
[KATE] Shh! Ahem!
I've been bad.
Chrono! Good morning!
[CHRONO yawns]
There you are, Rosette,
good morning.
Where's the Elder?
Where he always is...
in his workshop.
And I'm afraid the old coot's
been pulling another
all-nighter.
Oh, Sister Rosette.
All night and this
is all you made?
[ELDER] Yes, indeed!
I call it a "Spirit."
A Spirit, huh?
I'd appreciate it if
you could deliver it
to Sister Kate for me.
Sure thing!
Make sure it gets there!
Hey, what are you saying?
I've got sticky fingers?
You're one to talk,
Mister "Filched the Gospel
and made me promise
not to tell."
Goink.
[ELDER] Hm...
Well, to be honest,
I'd be much more at ease
if Chrono delivered it,
but given how much the
good Sister dislikes him...
It can't be helped,
sir. I mean I am a...
Oh bushwa and
horsefeathers!
What kind of devil
could be so charming
morning, noon, and night?
Not to mention one that
will do the cooking,
cleaning, and sometimes
even the windows?
But the fact is,
I frighten people.
Except for Rosette, that is.
So, what do you have
stuffed in here?
Oh, a teensy weensy devil.
--[ELDER laughs]
--[CHRONO] Huh?
[ROSETTE] Huh?
You see, at the moment of
impact, the devil is released,
producing an enormous
bolt of mystical energy
that strikes your enemy!
And what about the devil?
It's transformed into
a spiritual energy,
hence the name.
When that energy is
released, it goes "boom!"
and is annihilated.
I think... it would be
best not to use those.
Because there's
a devil inside?
[CHRONO] Mm.
Well, sympathy for the devil
aside, I'm sure the Elder
wouldn't make it if it was
dangerous. Right, sir?
[ELDER laughs]
Maybe I should
fire a test round.
[CHRONO] Rosette, a new case!
We've got marching orders!
[ROSETTE chuckles]
What a monster!
In the nick of time!
The Order of Magdalene,
we deliver!
Ah!
Give a girl some room, please.
Not you two again!
Rosette, if you
aim for the horn,
one of the Sacreds ought to be
strong enough to break it off!
Ah! I think all that
did was make it angrier!
Try to hit the
same spot again!
Well, this ought to finish it.
Ah! Rosette, that's
not a good idea!
Oh, don't worry.
Everything's jake.
It's the same plan
as before, remember?
Ah!
Huh? How could losing
its horn do that?
[CHRONO gasps]
[CHRONO] What is this?
What am I sensing?
[footsteps]
[DETECTIVE] Well,
as I said last time,
the two of you are really
something unique,
but at least this time
there's less damage.
[ROSETTE] Oh, it's not here!
[CHRONO] Then that can
only mean one thing!
What?
That it's not here.
Maybe we should try
searching a wider area.
That gun was loaded
with a Spirit, wasn't it?
[ROSETTE] Mm.
But why?
I just... thought that since
the one in the ship worked,
it wouldn't hurt to
have one just in case.
[growl]
So that's all, then?
It sounds exactly
like your last case.
[ROSETTE]
Well, we think this host
was a devil worshipper, too.
[KATE] I see.
A devil worshipper...
I'll prepare a report,
a very detailed one, ma'am.
And what became of
the devil's horn?
We submitted it
to the Elder, sir.
A very appropriate decision.
Oh, this is most
oddly disappointing.
Ma'am?
I believe this
was the first time
while hearing one of
your debriefings,
that I haven't shouted at you.
It's very nice, Sister,
very nice indeed.
Thank you very much, ma'am.
Yes, excellent work, Rosette.
I hope that you'll try
to make a habit of this.
[ROSETTE] Uh, yes, ma'am.
May I be excused?
Oh, why, why did
I lie to her?
Please, Lord, forgive me.
Huh?
It's Rosette.
[ELDER] Huh?
Hey, Rosette! The Elder
thinks he can make a detector
that will locate the Spirit
by its mystical aura.
I'm sorry, Elder.
Don't be so grummy,
it's not like you.
[ELDER] Oh, Remington!
So now I understand
what really happened.
[ROSETTE] I'm a bad girl.
Yes, from the way you were
acting around Sister Kate,
I thought something was wrong.
I can't lie to you,
Father Remington, can I?
No, but fortunately for
you, I can keep a secret.
So, how might I be of aid?
[POSSESSED] Who is there?
[POSSESSED] Hmm. Is it this?
The voice of the
hornless one...
I can hear it inside.
Children! It's done!
Mm-hmm. Ain't it
the gnat's whistle?
Do you really think
that thing's gonna work?
Perhaps there might
be a more reliable--
[ELDER] Such impertinence!
I gave it my seal of approval!
Switch, on!
Oh!
Elder?
Uh, it would seem that it's
much closer than we thought.
You don't think...
[ROSETTE] Mm.
[alarm bell rings]
[MILITIA MAN] Halt!
A man?
Proceed no further!
Identify yourself!
Where have you been?
[ROSETTE] We're sorry, sir.
An unnaturally thick aura of
evil surrounds that man, Sister.
Have your men
flank the intruder.
Lock and load with
Sacred rounds.
Make sure they know to
use only the Sacred type.
Right!
Class three and higher exorcists
support the militia's fire!
Right!
He's got an exorcist
special .45?
How could that gun be...?
Stop it! No!
--[REMINGTON] Ah!
--[CHRONO] Ah!
--[KATE] Ah!
--[ROSETTE] Ah!
Him again!
Yeah, the devil we
fought this afternoon!
Permission granted
to open fire!
No! Somehow, that
demon's absorbing
the power of the Spirit!
[ROSETTE] Huh?
He's used it to replace
the power of his broken horn!
Keep firing!
[CHRONO] Hey, you big eggplant!
Are you looking for
this ___? Come on!
Steady!
Concentrate your fire!
No, wait!
I'll take care of this, sir.
Rosette, come back here!
[ROSETTE] I've got you now!
Uh?
Uh?!
Rosette!
Ah!
[CHRONO screams]
[CHRONO] What have you done,
lowest of the low?
You so beneath my contempt,
you have not even a name!
You dare touch
my contractor?
You dare hurt what's mine?
Chrono...
Something's happening...
he's changing!
[KATE] Prepare to use Gospels!
But if Chrono and
Rosette are too close,
then using something as
powerful as a Gospel could...
[KATE] We cannot let
the seal be broken!
Don't forget what Chrono is!
No, Sister! At least wait
until Chrono's pulled back.
He no longer
possesses reason.
At this point,
he's a danger to us all.
And he's the most powerful
devil we've ever faced.
A devil?
If it... If it comes
to that, I swear I'll...
[ROSETTE] Come back, Chrono!
I'm all right! I'm all right!
[KATE] How can she trust
that creature so?
[ELDER] Ah, but Rosette doesn't
think of Chrono
as a devil, Sister.
But, how else
could one see it?
Just look. If you watch them,
I believe you'll understand.
I'm afraid all we can
do now is watch over them.
It's beginning.
[FIORE] Lord Joshua.
Ah, Fiore.
Lord Aion left a message
for you just now.
He said that he
would call again later.
You could have
called me, you know.
We seek Aion,
the Sinner!
I, the Viscount Borzo,
shall kill him myself!
I shall smash him with
one righteous blow!
[FIORE] You should go, please.
[FIORE] Hmm?
Not this time, my dear.
But, Lord Joshua...
Why don't you go
prepare the coffee?
I'll handle this trifle.
Still thy tongue!
It's not possible.
How can such power be?
What are you?
Have you injured
yourself, my Lord?
Ha! Oh, just a little nick.
[ANNA] Psst. Hey, did you hear?
Rosette and Chrono are
going on a trip together!
[MARY] What? I want to go!
[ANNA] I heard they're
going to a casino,
and they get to see
an opera, too!
[MARY] What? I want to do that!
[ANNA] And to top it all off,
they're going to stay at a ritzy
high class hotel... together!
[MARY] It's not fair!
Why only Rosette?
[CLAIRE] Oh, Rosette,
incarnation of destruction,
please, try not to
destroy anything.
[ANNA] Next episode, "Apostle."
[MARY] Oh, applesauce!
Another town's going
to vanish, isn't it?