[lightning strikes]
[phone rings]
[CHRONO] Um...
[ROSETTE snores]
Rosette... It's the phone,
Rosette... Wakey wakey!
[ROSETTE]
You get it, Chrono...
[CHRONO chuckles]
Are you sure, Rossette?
You know how Sister Kate
feels about me.
[ROSETTE] Mmmph!
Oh, rats!
Sorry, Chrono.
[CHRONO] Heh! It's Jake.
Phew.
Hello, this is
Sister Rosette!
[KATE] Too slow!
Go to the East Side immediately!
It's an emergency!
[ROSETTE] Right.
So what's the situation?
[KATE] The report says
that restaurant patrons
have been taken hostage.
It may be a failed summoning.
[ROSETTE] But what about the
other sisters or the militia?
[KATE] They're all currently
working other cases.
You're the one
closest to the scene,
so be prepared to
take immediate action!
[ROSETTE] What?!
But I just finished my last
mission a few hours ago!
I can't handle two in one night!
[KATE] Our order exists
to serve Sister Rossette!
There can be no rest for the
weary until the job's done!
Say... Why do you suppose Sister
Kate's always such a pill to me?
Heh. Could it be because
you're always doing things
that make her angry?
[ROSETTE] Hmph!!!
[CHRONO screams]
[COPPERS] Aaaaaa!
[DETECTIVE and COPPERS gasp]
[COPPERS chatter]
[CHRONO] Oh applesauce!
You've wrecked another jalopy!
Sister Kate's going to kill us!
[ROSETTE] Shh! Quit beating
your gums Chrono and help me...
Open this...
It won't open!
Lousy hayburning...
Hai-ya!
[DETECTIVE and COPPERS gasp]
[ROSETTE] Whew!
[ROSETTE and CHRONO] Huh?
[ROSETTE] Aaaaaa!
Oh, good I'm glad to see
everyone is here already.
Um... yes...
but who are you?
Sister Rosette Christopher,
Order of Magdalene,
at your service.
The wet blanket's
my assistant Chrono.
And that, is a warrant
from a federal judge.
The Order of Magdalene...?
[ROSETTE] Ready, Chrono?
Right!
So... As of right now,
we'll be taking over
jurisdiction of this case.
Just leave
everything to us, sir.
Ah... I see... so the two of you
are some kind of exorcists then?
[ROSETTE laughs]
Yep, we're the good guys!
[footsteps]
[POLICEMAN] Excuse me sir, but
just who are those young people?
[DETECTIVE] Professionals.
Monster exterminators.
[POLICEMAN] Monster
exterminators?!
I'd heard about a secret
organization the brass call in
to handle poltergeists
and demons...
but I never thought
they'd be so young...
So what are you feeling?
I sense a great hunger
that's been fed...
I'm afraid the hostages
are... well...
It's the bum's rush then!
Aaaaaa!
Ow... Jeez!
What in the heck did I just--
Aaaaaaaaaaa!
[CHRONO] Rosette!
His spiritual energy's
been consumed...
every bit of life sucked out...
mummifying him.
[ROSETTE] Hmph!
[ROSETTE] Chrono!
[CHRONO] Hm?
[door creaks]
[flies buzz]
A Satanist...?
Rich and stupid...
What a hobby!
[CHRONO] Thrillseekers,
seeking the ultimate thrill...
But when you play with hellfire
you're going to get burned,
just like this dumb sap...
[ROSETTE gasps]
Rosette!
[ROSETTE] Huh? Aaa!
Aaaaaa!
[ROSETTE] He's too fast!
You're just wasting those
Sacreds trying to slow him down!
Cut the bull and
do something!
[CHRONO] Rosette!
[CHRONO winces]
[shrieking]
[CHRONO gasps]
[gunshots]
Ack! Rosette something
bad is happening!
[ROSETTE] Huh? Aaaa!!
Aaaaaaaaaaa!
[ROSETTE AND CHRONO scream]
[DETECTIVE and COPPERS]
Aaaaaaaaaaa!!!!
[coughs]
[ROSETTE AND CHRONO gasp]
Rosette...
[ROSETTE] Huh?
You did it again!
[ROSETTE] Huh? Ack!
I-It wasn't me! Nooo!
Why is it always like this?!
[KATE] You did it again?!
We had hoped that this
time the destruction
would be kept to a minimum,
Sister Rosette,
and yet somehow...
Somehow, no matter what, you
always surpass our expectations.
Well I'm honored to
accept your praise, Ma'am.
I wasn't praising you!
Even the New York City Police
are lodging complaints
about you now!
Honestly, Sister Rosette,
can't you do better?
[ROSETTE] I'm sorry Sister Kate.
Rosette, could your "assistant"
be part of the problem?
[ROSETTE] Huh?
If one who lives in darkness
should call out to
that darkness...
Chrono had nothing
to do with this!
It's just that I...
wasn't strong enough!
I'll submit a written apology,
okay? Excuse me.
W-Wait! Come back
Sister Rosette! Please!
[ROSETTE] Hmm?
Ah... Sister Rosette.
Fa... Father Remington...!
When... did you
get back, sir?
Just now actually.
But I could hear you from
out in the vestibule...
More apologies is it?
[ROSETTE giggles]
I'm hitting on all sixes.
Father, please!
The last thing that girl
needs is coddling!
And as for you Rosette,
we're not finished talking yet!
I'm concerned
about that Devil's--
Perhaps you're are,
but I've got lots of written
apologies to write so goodbye!
[ROSETTE giggles]
[KATE] Sister Rosette!
[KATE sighs]
You're the only one that
girl is truly open with.
What is your report, Father?
I'm afraid that... this news
will not be very pleasant...
Hi, Chrono!
[CHRONO] Eep!
Is Rosette writing
more apologies?
Still I guess
that's what happens
when a Servant of God
destroys a whole building...
No, it was the whole block!
Huh? Really?!
Actually... I'd heard
it was a whole island?
Whaaaaa?! Really?!
It must be so hard.
[CHRONO sighs]
[CHRONO] Well, it happens
every time, so...
[ROSETTE] It happens
every time...?!
[MARY, ANNA, CLAIRE]
Aaah! Rosette!
A whole block was it...?
An island...?
Blowing someone's mistakes
out of proportion
is so much fun, isn't it?
But were you there?
Huh?! Huh? Huh?
[ANNA] We definitely don't
want to be teamed up with you!
[MARY, CLAIRE] Uh huh!
[ROSETTE] Go chase yourselves,
why don't you?!
Aaaaw! Applesauce!
[CHRONO] Rosette! Wait!
[KATE] I feel a great
unease, Father.
[REMINGTON] About him you mean?
No matter how docile that
creature may appear now,
it's still...
[REMINGTON] Yet, does a heart
not beat in his chest as well?
There are things one cannot
trust on faith alone.
But isn't faith the process
of affirming truths
that one cannot see?
Might it be that these
uncertain times are meant
to test our faith, Sister?
So the war could
be the cause then?
A cause, but not the only one.
Others will reveal
themselves soon enough...
'Til then, all we
can do is wait.
And as to what will
become of Chrono then...
I cannot even imagine...
[ROSETTE eats noisily]
[ROSETTE] Hmph! The nerve
of those Dumb Doras!
"We don't want to
team up with you!!"
I'm the one who'd
turn them down!
Gurp!
[ROSETTE gasps]
Gaaaaaa...
[slurping]
Hey, that holy water
burned your hand...
Yeah, but it helped us
defeat that thing.
Thank you.
[CHRONO] Hmm?
[CHRONO] Well,
we are... you know...
[ROSETTE] Oh...
I was having...
a dream...
before we went to
East Side... yesterday.
[CHRONO] Hm?
[ROSETTE] In my dream,
Joshua was still the way
I remember him.
Even though I know that...
for me to dream about him...
[CHRONO] This isn't like you...
[ROSETTE] Huh?
Rosette never
gets discouraged.
[ROSETTE laughs]
Thanks Chrono... for worrying.
Hmm?
[CHRONO] Hmm?
Hee hee! I see Paris. I see
France. I see someone's...!
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
And today's pair is almost
as white as the French flag!
[ROSETTE] You perverted old man!
I'll kill you with this spoon!
Ah, and how are
you today my boy?
[CHRONO] Uh, well...
Stop ignoring me! Huh?
Huh... What's this?
[ELDER] Oh, just
a little something
I finished this morning.
I call it the "Gospel."
Gospel?
[ELDER] Yes, a new
mystical bullet
composed of rare
alchemical silver with
ancient Enochian transcriptions
in microscopic text!
As such its destructive power is
much greater than the Sacred's,
which merely has holy oil
packed inside its explosive.
It's still in the
testing phase of course,
but I was going to ask the
Order's number one markswoman
to test fire it
for me... until...
Yes! Yes!
I wanna! I wanna!
You know this is the sort of
thing I looooooooove... Ack!
Having heard her call
the Saint responsible
for our Holy ammo
an old pervert,
perhaps I should
rethink this matter.
Hearing things,
you were hearing things.
Don't be mean.
Just let me try it. Come on!
Well, let me fondle
your luscious breasts
and I'll rethink my position...
[SISTER A] Sister Rosette?
[ROSETTE] Who would let
you fondle anything?!
[SISTER A] Sister Kate
is calling for you.
Come to her office at once.
Sounds like
marching orders!
How sad that this
will have to wait...
You Scrooge!
[sirens blare]
[horn honks]
[COPPERS] Aaaaaa! Look out!
[tires screech]
[CHRONO] Well at least...
this time you didn't wreck the
car playing Barney Oldfield.
[ROSETTE] Chrono! Stop being
a Mrs. Grundy and dry up!
[COMMANDER] Are you the ones
from the Magdalene Order?
I'm afraid that I'd hoped that
there'd be more than two of you.
I'm sorry but due to an
occurrence in Boston,
we've had to
split our forces.
However, as I work with
the effort of ten men
I assure you
things will be fine!
Um... well I guess we have
no choice but to believe that.
Good, 'cause only those
who believe will be saved.
So they say, get it?
[CHRONO laughs faintly]
[COMMANDER] All we know is that
the ship's registry is British
and that we've lost contact
with the rescue party
we sent on board.
[FIREFIGHTER A]
Hey Chief! Chief!
There's a survivor! Look!
Great Jehoshaphat!
[SAILOR] Help! Save me!
[FIRE CHIEF, FIREFIGHTERS gasp]
[roars]
I'm sensing... rage and wrath.
An indescribable anger
gives form to its actions...
But behind that...
there's a separate consciousness
moving it... something...
[CHRONO] Who is it?
[ROSETTE] Chrono!
[CHRONO] Huh?
[ROSETTE] What's wrong with you?
Let's make like Sergeant York!
[CHRONO] Right!
Hey wait! You can't
go in there alone!
[COMMANDER, FIRE CHIEF,
and FIREFIGHTERS gasp]
[ROSETTE] Arr!
[ROSETTE AND CHRONO yell]
Rosette if we don't hurry
we're going to be--!
Chrono! Get this boat
back away from the docks!
Oh yeah sure. No problem!
It'll be duck soup...
That bruiser sure did
a number on this place.
[CHRONO] All right, then.
[CHRONO grunts]
[ROSETTE grunts]
[gasps]
What in the world was
this ship carrying?
Aaaaaaa! Aaaaaa!
[FIRE CHIEF, COPPERS,
AND FIREFIGHTERS yell]
It's headed to sea!
[CHRONO] This must be it.
[CHRONO grunts]
Aaaa!
[ROSETTE yells]
[CHRONO yells]
[CHRONO] Oh, gosh darn it!
[ROSETTE] Waaah!
Why don't you drop dead?!
[ROSETTE] If it's
Astrally based...
...then the Sacred
ought to be enough!
[gun clicks]
[ROSETTE] Eh? Eh!
Chrono!
I'll unleash the seal!
[CHRONO] You can't! This power
will summon forth more violence!
A Gospel!
[CHRONO]
Please don't tell the Elder!
Ahhhh!
[ROSETTE] A-Aaaaa!
[ROSETTE] Bring peace
to the lost lambs!
I bid thee give rest
to the fangs of the wolf!
And call a hammer
of death unto the devil!
Can wisdom... ever
truly overcome violence?
[CHRONO] Is that it's true form?
It was stolen.
Taken from
its home...
Even so that's no reason
to hurt so many people...
Aaa! Oh no!
Huh?
[ROSETTE] Waugh! Huh?
Aaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Chrono! Do you realize
what you've done?
[CHRONO] Well, the boat wasn't
responding to the helm,
and the engine was all
balled up so what could I do?
[ROSETTE AND CHRONO] Waugh!
[ROSETTE] I'm not the bad one!
Why is it always, always,
always like this?!
[ROSETTE] Chrono!
What'll I do? What'll I do?
[CHRONO] Oh great,
what did you destroy this time?
[ROSETTE] Nothing! But I lost
something very important!
[CHRONO] What do you mean,
"something very important"?
[ROSETTE] When a girl talks
about something very important,
isn't it obviously
what she means?
[CHRONO] Wha...? You couldn't
possibly mean that, could you?
[ROSETTE] Why are
you turning red?
Oh! You nasty devil!
[CHRONO] Next episode,
"Contractor."
[ROSETTE] Oh Lord, please
save these lost lambs!