Here you go!
[ghostly moan]
Ahh!
[BILLY]
Can't catch me!
[SEIRA] Hey!
Kevin, come back here and
help us with the chores!
It's you and Billy's
turn to do it today!
[NELLY]
It's your turn!
[SEIRA] Honestly!
[NELLY] Honestly!
--Huh?
Hello you two.
Sister Azmaria!
Sister!
[JEAN] As you can see, the
children are doing wonderfully.
As always, thank you for
everything you've done.
[KATE] Oh no,
it's wonderful to see
that the children
are doing so well.
[JEAN] Mhmm. From the
moment we were revived,
it's been just like before.
I'm certainly glad that we're
living here in the country.
Four years have
passed in New York,
so I'm sure it's
changed quite a bit.
Yes, it has.
[JEAN sighs]
By the way, has Rosette...
[KATE] No, we still
haven't found her.
What a shame.
Please Sister,
sing us a song!
But I haven't even finished
reading you the
story yet, Nelly.
I'd like to hear you
sing, too, Sister.
I don't know why,
but for some reason,
when I hear you sing
it really relaxes me.
But... my power is gone.
[SEIRA]
You've said that before.
It was called
spiritual power, right?
But that isn't
exactly what I mean.
It's just that it makes me
feel warm inside when you sing.
Your song echoes
in my heart.
It really does.
It really does!
Thank you, Seira, Nelly.
In that case I'll sing!
[NELLY] Wah!
♪ Lo, He comes with
clouds descending ♪
♪ Once for favored
sinners slain ♪
♪ Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! Hallelujah! ♪
♪ God appears on
Earth to reign... ♪
I'm certainly glad
Sister Azmaria is here.
She's a godsend.
Her singing voice
is remarkable,
and it has such a wonderful
effect on the children.
Actually though,
she keeps telling me that
she wants to become a Sister,
exactly like Rosette.
Oh yes, there's something
I forgot to tell you.
Yesterday, the children said
they want to go
and visit Joshua.
You mean take
them to New York?
But if they see
him as he is now,
they're certain to feel
the difference in time.
I imagine they are simply trying
to help Joshua in their own way.
And after all, we cannot avert
our eyes from reality forever.
Remington, have you
been down here before?
[REMINGTON] Once before,
when I first brought Rosette
and Chrono to the Order.
If you knew this
place was here,
then why didn't you
tell me about it?
I'm sorry, it was
because I had to conceal
the knowledge of Magdalene
deep within myself.
I see.
I did the same.
Just as I thought.
Rosette and Chrono did
come here, after all.
[ELDER] It's been
a while, Magdalene...
But I imagine
I'll be coming along
to join you before too long.
[REMINGTON gasps]
[ELDER] Huh?!
[ELDER] Horns!
Are they Chrono's?
No. More than likely,
they belong to Aion.
But what are
they doing here?
[REMINGTON] Perhaps Magdalene
made an effort to calm Aion,
and Rosette and Chrono
are both so kind.
[gasps]
So that's the answer.
[ELDER]
Huh?
[REMINGTON] Aion's horns
have the power to move time...
the exact opposite of Chrono's.
The release of
the time freeze
could never have
been accomplished
without using the power
of Aion's horns.
Just what are
you trying to do?
[ELDER] Because of
what this place is,
I thought Rosette might be here.
But no good.
It's ironic, isn't it...
that we needed
our enemy's power?
Aion's power wasn't
just moving time.
His deeds have advanced
the times themselves.
[REMINGTON]
Although its span was brief,
the overabundance of faith
in Rosette's stigmata
gripped the entire country
and blurred the line between
justice and violence.
[ELDER] A realization of
the second Prophecy.
A great war will begin...
in the near future without fail.
I wonder why your
boss won't stop it.
Why? I've no
desire to ask.
So you really hate
Him now, do you?
Oh, I have no
hatred for Him.
I have simply ended
our relationship.
I've no attachment
to torn wings.
But by losing them,
you will acquire an even
heavier cross to bear.
It's the least I can
do as an atonement.
[DETECTIVE B] The Crusaders
just keep rolling in.
They still claim it's
all for the Holy Woman
and the revolution.
Fortunately, there isn't
any lateral communication yet,
but I shudder to think what will
happen when they come together
and start this Crusade
they've been waiting for.
That'll be a right mess.
[PRISONER A] Is that
the Holy Woman?!
[ANNA] Ahh!
Pipe down, you!
That's enough!
[PRISONER A] They dare to put a
Crusader in a place like this?!
They're agents of the devils!
Bring down Heaven's punishment!
[PRISONER B] She's here?!
[PRISONER C]
The Holy Woman is here!
[PRISONER D]
The Holy Woman!
And the worst thing is
it isn't over yet.
[MARY]
Mm-hmm.
Stop the car!
[MARY] Rosette!
Mary!
Wait! Rosette, wait!
Rosette!
Excuse me?
Oh, I'm so sorry. I thought
you were someone else.
Mary...
I'm sure that she'll
be back some day.
After all, she is
Rosette you know.
So, let a smile be
your umbrella, okay?
[MARY] Okay.
[door opens]
[typing sounds]
I'm back.
[CLAIRE]
Oh, welcome home, Father.
You forget that I'm not
a minister anymore, Claire.
I'm sorry, sir.
[REMINGTON] Hmm?
Oh, Joshua was working on
this picture a few hours ago,
but then he stopped
to write a story.
[REMINGTON]
A story, eh?
[CLAIRE] Yes, I think this
was one of the illustrations.
[REMINGTON]
So, Joshua...
Oh, hi Ewan.
[REMINGTON]
You're writing a story, huh?
[JOSHUA]
Mhmm, an adventure novel.
Well, you've always wanted to
become a novelist, haven't you?
[JOSHUA]
Yeah, but it's pretty hard.
But Sister Claire taught me
how to use the typewriter
and I'm finally
getting the hang of it.
And would this drawing
be one of the scenes
from the novel
you're working on?
That's right!
This part here is
called the Astral Line.
See it's this great river of
life that flows through space.
[REMINGTON] Did you think
that up yourself?
[JOSHUA] Of course.
This girl is the main character.
She's very strong,
and in order to defeat the bad
guys who want the Astral Line,
she goes on a journey
to battle them with
her younger brother and her
partner who's from outer space.
It sounds interesting.
You really think so?!
Well, then when I'm finished,
will you read it first?
[REMINGTON]
O-Of course!
Claire, thank you for today.
Give Sister Kate my regards.
Sure, I'll tell her.
Will he stay like this?
Will Joshua have the heart
of a twelve year old forever?
Caught between God and Man,
he destroyed his own heart
in order to protect himself.
Joshua is proof of my sin.
But you can't
mean that, sir.
[REMINGTON]
I am... a Sinner.
Rosette, where are you?
[CHRONO] Rosette...
Come sit with me,
the sun's so warm today.
You know, I really
do like this view.
I wish that I could just
go on looking at it forever.
[ROSETTE] Hey...
[CHRONO] Hm?
[ROSETTE] I was thinking
about undoing the seal.
If I did it, then you could
heal all of your wounds,
and everything would be jake.
[CHRONO]
Oh, applesauce, Rosette.
Being here with you is what's
really important right now.
And I don't want to
lose anything else...
...not ever again.
I think about them sometimes and
wonder how everyone is doing.
[CHRONO] Uh-huh.
But for right now, I'd rather
just be here with you.
In these last few months
we've spent together,
I've wanted to say
so many things to you,
but the words
just won't come.
[CHRONO]
Let's go back inside.
I think you should
lie down and rest.
[ROSETTE] But I don't
want to rest yet.
Not yet.
I'm just...
[sobbing]
...so scared, Chrono!
[ROSETTE] I'm scared!
I don't want to die!
[sobbing]
I... just want to
live a little longer.
Is that so wrong?
Oh, Rosette...
[ROSETTE cries]
[ticking]
Chrono...
[ROSETTE] Thank you.
[ticking stops]
[phone rings]
Yes?
[gasps]
Where are they?
[crying sounds]
[AZMARIA sobs]
[REMINGTON]
They found them?
But it's been so long.
[KATE] Yes, nearly
six months in fact.
But it appears that the two of
them found some happiness first.
Remington, I have to
ask you something.
And what is it?
[KATE] Will the soul of someone
who has made a contract
with a devil be
condemned to Hell?
No, that's just superstition.
Thank you. Thank you
for saying that.
That girl... truly believed.
Even though she
contracted with a devil...
She always followed
the teachings of mercy.
I believe Rosette's soul
was the most virtuous spirit
that I will ever know.
Remington, do you have
any desire to come back?
I'm afraid I can't, Sister.
[KATE]
I understand.
But Remington, I will
not abandon my faith.
Yes, I see. I thought
that you would say that.
Thank you for telling
me, Sister Kate.
You're working
rather hard, Joshua.
[JOSHUA]
Of course I am!
I have to finish drawing it so
you can look at it, don't I?
There's no need
to be in a rush.
I have all the time
in the world to wait.
It won't that long,
I'll be done real soon 'kay?
[REMINGTON] Sure.
[REMINGTON] And the times
continue to move.
As we head toward
the second Prophecy,
things are approaching
the boiling point.
In Chicago, the Saint
Valentine's Day Massacre...
in Berlin, Bloody May Day...
in Jerusalem, the
Wailing Wall Incident...
and Black Thursday.
The worst crash ever to hit
the New York Stock Exchange.
It stirred up
uncertainty and despair
and inspired a rash of suicides.
Its impact will be felt
throughout the world.
In Germany,
a rising faction is calling
for general conscription.
This era is clearly trying to
choose the path to turmoil.
Why? So many people
will die again.
Why?
[KATE] Can this
truly be Your will?
At least Rosette and
the others were spared
from seeing what is to come...
the Prophecy...
the one of war that is
soon to be fulfilled.
In that, one could say,
that they were truly blessed.
[knocking]
Come in.
Yes, what is it?
There's a report
from the Miami branch.
They say another person
with stigmata has appeared.
Stigmata?
[KATE] Is this the
revelation of a new age?
[AION] It is the dawn
of a wondrous age.
I am the Alpha and the Omega,
the beginning and the end.
One plot has
been completed,
in order to open the next door.
[AZMARIA] Rosette, Chrono,
I will become stronger!
So please, watch
over me, okay?
[REMINGTON]
Great forefathers...
Just like you, I am
a spectator to this era,
until I have atoned for my sins.
I will live forever.
[thud]
[AION] I am eternity
given birth by desire,
the shadow cast by God.
Pandemonium was
filled with light,
and Heaven with darkness.
Look at the times.
No matter how hard
people struggle,
their fates are in our hands.
[gunshot]