[gunfire]
[tires screech]
[gunfire continues]
[howling]
Ahhh!
[crash]
Nuttin' stops it!
A-Aaahhh!
[DETECTIVE] Three days.
This calamity has occurred
in just three days.
First it was the
Jayrock gang...
and yesterday
the Bogard family.
That's two Mafia clans...
completely slaughtered
by the same creature,
and all the survivors
say that the attacker
was some kind of
enormous hound...
a dog with
glowing blue eyes.
Did you just say blue eyes?
That's right.
And it's not something
that our officers can
possibly fight, Sister.
Tell me, do you know what
kind of creature this is?
This black dog...
is not of this world.
Relax, Detective. It's fine.
The Magdalene Order
is taking action,
even as we speak.
Geez! This is
totally ridiculous!
We're going over fifty,
and we still can't catch it!
Hold on!
[MAFIOSO B]
Can't this heap go any faster?
[howling]
[gunfire]
Take the wheel! Now!
[CHRONO] Right!
I missed! But how?
I think the bullets
passed right through it.
[ROSETTE] Huh?
Ahhh!
Ahh!
Rosette!
Cut him to pieces,
my brave May!
Mutigster!
[SATELLA] It's getting much
closer to becoming corporeal.
I should be able
to finish it off...
...next time.
Satella...
Hey, what's that German
Jezebel doing here?
[CHRONO] Oh, for
crying out loud,
just turn the gas
down, all right?
Ands-hay Off-ay.
I wanna know
what she's up to!
Rosette!
[groaning]
I'll call for a medic while you
handle the survivor, all right?
[ROSETTE] Right!
Hold on! Just hold on
a little longer!
No, hold on!
Don't give up!
Please!
[ROSETTE sobs]
[KATE] Now then, militia,
the true identity
of the creature
Sister Rosette encountered
in Manhattan last night
has been revealed via evidence
found at another crime scene.
[REMINGTON] Bianca Winger.
Female. Age twenty-two.
Using black magic, she
appears to have sacrificed
her own life in order
to summon a hellhound,
for the purpose of slaughtering
New York's Cosa Nostra--
the Mafia.
This gruesome trail of carnage
appears to be all her doing.
But why?!
Vengeance, of course.
Or, more concisely, for love.
What we have learned so far
is that about six months ago,
a Richard Smith,
Bianca's fiancé, was caught
in a gun battle between
the Mafia and the police,
and was killed
in the crossfire.
[whispered]
Her fiancé...
Such is the heart that
sometimes the greatest of loves
can be transformed
into purest hate.
[KATE sighs]
I feel such pity for her,
and for the pain
that she had to bear.
Our problem now is that
the creature she summoned
happens to be an Astral spirit.
It has been created from
Bianca's negative emotions,
her sadness,
hatred, and despair.
And as such, its existence is
like an arrow without substance.
So you're saying we can't
attack it with standard weapons
or imprison it
with our barriers.
And as the creature continues
to consume more victims,
its body will grow larger
and more corporeal.
[GOTTI laughs]
[GOTTI]
You know, I gotta say
this hellhound is turnin'
out to be the berries!
Really? You're glad a monster
is trying to kill you?
Well you see,
thanks to the Jayrock and
Bogard gangs being bumped off,
this town's gonna be
a lot easier to work in.
[SATELLA] Heh.
But still, you ought to be
worried about your own safety.
Don't forget... if that
hellhound does become corporeal,
my presence may not
save you, Don Gotti.
It will require more
than some token offerings
if you want to
sleep peacefully,
and not with the fishes,
so to speak.
But that is why you
are here, jewel witch.
You are my body guard,
Satella Harvenheit!
As for offerings, I'll
make as many as are needed.
Ice in your veins, eh?
But I suppose that's
part of being a Godfather.
Heh. Miss Satella,
there are some times
when a man must make
choices, tough choices,
for the sake
of his family.
For family. How quaint.
[GOTTI] In order to
protect something,
certain sacrifices
are inevitable.
Do you capisce?
I can't say I disagree,
not with your way of
thinking anyway.
[GOTTI] I bet you don't.
[GOTTI guffaws]
[ROSETTE] I'm sorry,
but this whole plan
just rubs me the wrong way.
We can't delay our attack
until the black dog
completely materializes!
It's as if you're
telling us to sit back
and watch people get
killed until then!
Tell me, exactly
what alternatives
do we have in this situation,
Sister Rosette?
How do you propose
to fight a creature
that can run eighty miles an
hour and has no physical body.
Well, I didn't say I had an
answer to the problem just yet!
But, I just can't
stand back and watch!
Even when they're
all gangsters,
I just can't stand by
silently and watch
as they're all
slaughtered like this.
I'm sorry, I just
can't do that!
As it stands, this is
our only viable option.
The matter has been
decided in council
by the leaders of
the Magdalene Order.
[ROSETTE] Well that's
just not good enough!
Excuse me, please.
Uh, wait a minute,
Sister Rosette!
This discussion
hasn't been completed!
[door closes]
[KATE] Uh.
[sighs]
That girl is seriously...
Oh, she's certainly learned
to speak up, hasn't she?
I'm sure that
sense of justice...
comes from her belief in
the values we represent.
[ROSETTE]
Wow, now that is darb!
[ELDER] It's a super
high-speed transport!
I call it the Elder's
"Gabriel Hound."
[ROSETTE]
Woo! Ha, ha, ha!
We've been waiting on
you to fix our car,
and when I realized we
hadn't seen you in a while,
I figured we ought to
come over and take a peep.
But who would have
expected something like this?
[engine starts]
Woo! Ha, ha, ha!
Vroom vroom!
Yahoo!
[CHRONO laughs lightly]
Hey, how much juice does
this sweetheart's engine pump?
With 1500 cc's?
She's rock steady at ninety!
I used the latest iron chassis
from Harley as a base,
and then added my latest secret
speed-increasing technology.
Hey.
Ah, you've noticed.
Press that button,
and you'll engage
a special two-time rocket
booster for super acceleration!
It's the bees knees all right!
With this, we'll finally be able
to catch that black monster!
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
I didn't make this
machine for the Order!
What?! You mean I
don't get to keep it?
[ELDER laughs]
But if you let me fondle your
breasts, I'll lend it to you.
[thonk]
[ELDER yells]
Rosette, it's terrible!
Huh?
Not again, it's
that same old bull!
Well that's too bad
for you, copper!
[DETECTIVE] Hey, why
isn't the backup here yet?
[POLICEMAN] They're heading
this way right now!
[GOTTI] Huh?
Ah! Ahh! Ahhhh!
[ROSETTE] Did you say
it's in the subway?
[ELDER]
That's right!
The black beast turned
the whole Gotti family
into veal scaloppini
and escaped into a subway
tunnel at Grand Central Station.
It was last seen heading
west toward Penn Station
ahead of schedule!
The order sent
out the militia,
and is setting up a
concentric series of traps
radiating out from that
point, but the odds are
that our crucifix
barriers won't stop him.
Kommen sie!
I bid you take form!
Juwel ritters!
[SATELLA]
Cut him down!
Mutigster!
[motorcycle passes]
[girls yell]
Woo-hoo! I love the sights
of the lower East side!
[gasps]
[howling]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[bullet shells clatter]
Phew!
Ahh!
Ahhh!
Why in the hell are
there two of them now?!
How should I know?!
But it's already split,
so it can't be helped!
And how...
did it split?!
Well, it should
have been solid,
but my projections were off.
And why, oh why is it,
everything you do
ends up causing me
grief one way or another.
What did you say?!
[ROSETTE] Chrono,
let's get after the one
that's still out there.
[CHRONO whimpers]
That's not possible.
Aahh!
Oh, for crying out loud!
[ROSETTE]
What are we going to do?
We can't catch the
hellhound with this.
Chrono, have you
contacted the Elder?
It's no use.
I can't get through.
We're too far out of range
down here in the tunnels.
Great.
Don't forget what's driving
the black dog's appetite--
a curse that won't
end until its eaten
every two-bit
crook in New York.
No one can stop
that monster now.
--Why?
--Huh?
Why... do you always give up
on everything so quickly?
Why is that?
No matter how much
trouble I'm in,
even when I'm in pain,
I won't give up. I won't!
And neither should you!
But why should I do that?
The gangsters being killed are
the worst kind of human trash
who thoroughly deserve
everything they're
getting now and more.
Narcotics. Robbery. Murder.
Can you deny this is
their just reward?
And so what?
Even if these are people
who have committed crimes,
no one deserves to die.
Especially like that.
Hmph. Such sweet words.
However, you'll soon learn
these vermin know
nothing of your God.
To put their quarrels aside
and love their enemy is
beyond their measure.
If it's in their own interest,
it doesn't matter who
has to live or die.
Are you honestly
telling me that
you're willing to risk your
life for people like that?
Hmph!
What hypocrisy.
But I expect that
from you Sisters.
One should think
about oneself
before one thinks
about others, I say.
That's the only rational
philosophy of life
a sane person can have.
That's true.
Everything
you've said...
...could prove
right in the end.
[gasps]
[ROSETTE] However...
...the fact that it might,
just makes me madder.
Because the truth is, I don't
care what you might call me...
what names others
use behind my back.
My heart won't let
me let them die,
not when I can stop it.
So, of these things
that you summon,
which ones are
really fast?
[SATELLA] Huh?
Let me show you just how far
being in denial can take you.
This is jake!
You're insane!
And you drive
like a lunatic!
--[ROSETTE] That's right!
--[SATELLA] Ahh!
Rosette... you are
so off your nut.
There he is!
Get ready!
Keep it on course!
Are you giving me orders?
[yells in German]
It's no use shooting
from behind.
[ROSETTE grunts]
Satella, you better
hold on tight,
I'm going to get in
front of him for an attack!
What?! Just what
are you doing?
[ROSETTE] Here we go!
No good, he's much too fast!
He hasn't beaten us yet!
One more time!
[ROSETTE] Bring peace
to the lost lambs.
Give rest eternal to
the fangs of the wolf.
And call the hammer of
death unto the devil.
[howling]
Ahh!
What the...?!
[crashing and clattering]
Ah!
Rosette!
[screaming]
[ROSETTE coughs]
[ROSETTE]
What a smell!
[coughing]
But... admit it, it
turned out well, didn't it?
[ROSETTE chuckles]
To be honest,
I don't know
how much more
of you I can take.
Hey! Haven't you
forgotten somebody?
Hello? I'm talking about me!
You have forgotten me,
haven't you?
[MARY] Christmas!
Christmas! Christmas!
It only comes once a year!
Isn't it great?
[ANNA] Azmaria's the lead
in this year's Nativity play.
It's so exciting!
[CLAIRE] But it looks like
Rosette and the others
are planning something.
[ANNA] Could it be that
the tree will blow up?
[MARY] Maybe a devil will pop
out of one of our presents!
[CLAIRE] Let's pray
that we'll be able
to usher in Christmas
safely this year.
[ANNA and MARY]
Heaven help us!
[ANNA] Next episode,
"Holy Night."
[MARY] Come what may,
it's Christmas!