[frantic yelling]
[CHRONO] Rosette...
[GIRL]
Are you Chrono?
Um, yeah.
[GIRL] Here. This is from the
man who's with the Holy Woman.
[CHRONO gasps]
[CHRONO] Gimme that!
[GIRL] Ah!
It's from Rosette...
[bell rings]
[door creaks open]
Rosette!
[CHRONO groans]
Rosette, I read your letter,
but I don't understand!
You said you wanted me to
give something back to you...
What did you mean?
[AION]
She means her time.
[CHRONO]
I asked her!
[inaudible]
I want back... my lost time.
[CHRONO gasps]
Ooh, she wants to
cancel your contract.
[ROSETTE] I want
to save everyone.
And such a fitting
place to be released
from a deal with a devil,
don't you agree?
Stop playing
with our hearts!
Playing with your
hearts? Not moi.
The one who's playing with you
is that great heavenly hypocrite
who's always
standing idly by.
How unfaithful
you are, Chrono.
You still have feelings
for Magdalene,
and yet here you are pursuing
Rosette Christopher.
Hmph. Oh well, lust is one of
the cardinal sins, after all.
But I suppose you would
call it love, wouldn't you?
If that's how you feel,
then why are you here?
Can't you see that Rosette
would be so much better off
if you were dead?
As long as you live,
her life continues to
tick, tick, tick away.
I see... you are truly
determined to kill Rosette...
taking the life of
the woman you love
is becoming something of
a habit with you, isn't it?
Have you ever considered
changing your name
to the God of Death?
I've heard enough!
Why won't you
give it back to me?
[CHRONO gasps]
Why don't you
just kill him?
[CHRONO screams]
[CHRONO]
Why? Back then... why?
[AION] So, what became of that
woman you seduced earlier?
I grew weary of her.
[AION] This era amuses me.
So many choose to walk
the path to destruction.
It means the time is right.
[CHRONO] Yes.
[AION] So much corruption,
it makes me shiver.
[CHRONO] It's quite
an aphrodisiac.
[AION] God's absence
has blurred the line
between Pandemonium and Earth.
People can hear
only our voices now.
They have found
that lust and pleasure
provide opportunities
that prayer cannot.
Heaven is pitiful.
Humans were given hearts and
minds, yet because they think,
His light can no
longer reach them.
[CHRONO]
But it can reach us.
[AION] Pandemonium is nothing
more than God's contractor...
a clown who praises Heaven.
[CHRONO] Being a clown
is a sad existence.
They excite us and let us
sharpen our fangs and claws.
We will sacrifice
the world of man.
[CHRONO gasps]
With the clown's head
and the maiden who is most
beloved by God in our arms,
we will use the language
and violence of man
to make Heaven into Earth
and Earth into Heaven.
But that's...
The word for it is "sin."
But I call it freedom.
Freedom...
[AION] We will conceal the
marks of being incomplete,
and as truly complete beings,
recreate the world.
[CHRONO] If only...
I hadn't taken his hand.
[REMINGTON]
Where's Rosette?
[horn honks]
[frantic yelling]
[ELDER] The impudence!
It's despicable!
They're saying that
the Magdalene Order
is a band of heretics.
It's malice
masquerading as justice.
[ELDER] Thanks to
Gilliam's connections,
we'll be guests
here for a few days.
Sister Kate is trying
to return to New York.
Hmm... Thinking of Rosette, eh?
At this rate, I fear
she will become a martyr.
[ELDER] Yes, and Joshua as well.
Oh, hello.
If you came to see the Astral
Line, you're just in time.
It's already really close,
so it shouldn't be long.
I just hope my big
sister gets here soon.
If we don't explore it now,
we won't get another chance.
What's that?
[CHRONO] Father Remington
brought them back to me.
They're my horns.
Satella... and Fiore...
and Mr. Steiner...
I killed all of them.
They're dead because
I chose freedom.
When Aion cut off
Pandemonium's head,
I should have killed him.
None of this would
have happened
if I had been strong enough to
overcome my desire for freedom.
If I didn't exist...
[AZMARIA gasps]
[AZMARIA] Sister Kate.
[door closes]
[PHOTOGRAPHER]
Um, pardon me, Miss.
I thought I
recognized you.
You're the young lady from
the carnival, aren't you?
And let me tell you,
I sure was surprised
to find out that the girl
with you was the Holy Woman!
And you are...?
[PHOTOGRAPHER]
Oh, excuse me, Sister.
I work for a local
photography studio.
I tried at the Magdalene Order,
but it was verklempt.
I've been looking all over
for you and your friends.
Here, your picture is ready.
[PHOTOGRAPHER] And, um...
there's something else.
I happened to see the Holy
Woman in town the other day,
and I took a picture.
I just had to
show it to you.
[KATE gasps]
How horrible...
[PHOTOGRAPHER] You know,
it'll be a long time before
San Francisco is rebuilt,
but I'm going to photograph
every stage of its rebirth.
With everything that's
going on in this country,
the times we're
living in right now...
I just want to leave
my pictures behind
until the next
generation, you know?
See ya!
Wait a minute!
Um... What I mean is...
thank you very much for this.
[AZMARIA] This is proof.
Proof of that precious moment
when we were all still together.
Thank you for
leaving it behind.
[REMINGTON] Sister Kate...
[KATE]
Where's Rosette?
She's vanished.
Now we're back to square one.
Maybe not.
What is that?
[KATE] A picture of Rosette
that a local cameraman took.
[ELDER] Hmm?
This is completely...
[REMINGTON] I suspect Aion
is using the disturbances
in San Francisco as a test
for those who've
succumbed to despair.
Rosette's stigmata are
a powerful source of hope.
Aion will use that
hope as a weapon
to guide this country to
the brink of total chaos.
[KATE] And what will
await us if he succeeds?
The realization of the
second Prophecy of Fatima.
An even greater war.
[REMINGTON] I believe
we are being tested.
[KATE] For what?!
What exactly is the Lord
trying to make us do here?
[ROSETTE] I bid thee, bring
peace to the lost lambs,
give rest to the
fangs of the wolf,
and call the hammer of
death unto the devil!
[AION] There are no
virtuous people, not a one.
There are no
enlightened men.
There are no humans
who turn to God.
All have gone astray,
and nothing restrains them.
There is no virtue.
It is dead.
Within the last four weeks,
more than two hundred riots have
broken out across the country.
The police alone
cannot control it,
so the National Guard
has been mobilized,
and not even the
police are immune.
[gunshots]
Ahh! Ahhh!
[DETECTIVE]
I can still hear it.
I can hear the noise.
The noise?
[KATE] Yes. He claims to
hear the voices of devils.
[CHAIRMAN] Devils?
[KATE] Correct.
He seems to think that someone
is trying to trick him.
And there's more, sir.
Explain
these wounds!
[DETECTIVE]
These wounds protect me.
From what?
[DETECTIVE] I carved the
seals of the Holy Woman
into my body to protect
myself from the noise.
Only there are still
too many people
who make me hear the noise.
I will kill all of
them and become free!
And when you've
gained your freedom...
what happens then?
What did the Holy
Woman tell you?
[DETECTIVE]
That Heaven becomes Earth
and Earth will become Heaven!
[REMINGTON] And where does
the Holy Woman appear?
Wherever the Holy Woman
decides to appear.
We Crusaders just
do as she says.
[CHAIRMAN] Crusaders?
[KATE] Yes. Those who inflict
the stigmata upon themselves
refer to it as a sign
of the new Crusade.
Therefore, the warriors who bear
these marks upon their skin
call themselves Crusaders.
[CHAIRMAN sighs]
They are just common
killers in the end.
[KATE] Perhaps, but they
qualify their actions
by claiming it is a
battle for justice.
[CHAIRMAN] Justice?
[KATE] So they say.
Yet in truth,
it is only violence that
has spun out of control.
[CHAIRMAN] And Sister Rosette
is at the center of all this?
Where is she?
Unfortunately, we have
not found her.
[AZMARIA sighs]
[CHRONO winces]
These wounds...
they just won't heal.
Is this the same
kind of pain
that I've inflicted upon
you for all these years?
Why won't you give
it back to me?
[CHRONO]
What can I do to make up for
everything that
I've put you through?
What can I do?
[ROSETTE]
Chrono is still alive.
[AION] He wants to kill you,
no matter what the cost.
And you'll die
without saving anyone.
[ROSETTE]
That cannot be.
I will take back
my own life myself.
Bring him here one more time.
Good girl.
[AION] Can't you see
that Rosette would be
so much better off
if you were dead?
As long as you live,
her life continues to
tick, tick, tick away.
[CHRONO] I'm a devil.
Even if I'm given comfort,
all I can do is take.
So that in the end...
[AZMARIA]
Are regrets all you have?
[CHRONO] Azmaria?
You're not the only one
with regrets, you know!
I couldn't help her either!
And now, Rosette is
suffering by herself!
But it isn't exactly--
[AZMARIA]
The two of us are the same!
We both fought
alongside Rosette!
[CHRONO gasps]
And Miss Satella, too.
Maybe there was something
I could have done to help her,
but... now it's too late
to change any of it!
But... the friendship...
the time we've had
together means something!
Look! You can't deny even
the good things we shared!
You can't pretend that those
precious moments didn't exist.
I can keep going because
I have you with me.
It's because my time is limited
that I don't have any doubts.
[ROSETTE]
Chrono!
[CHRONO] I came back to
protect Rosette, but...
[ROSETTE] I will save him...
no matter what!
[CHRONO]
Rosette never ran away.
But I ran from Pandemonium...
and from Aion...
and from Magdalene's sadness.
And I was about
to do it again.
Chrono?
[CHRONO] Azmaria...
I have to stop running
and finish this myself.
And no matter what, I'll
bring Rosette back this time!
Chrono!
Good for you! I've been
waiting to hear you say that.
Elder...
[ELDER chuckles]
I made this in preparation
for this very day.
It can mystically and
scientifically deduce
the whereabouts of a
person from the traces
that were left behind on
something they've used!
Now, hand me that gun, Chrono.
[CHRONO] Uh, sure.
Ah!
W-What's going on here?!
I haven't even started
the thing yet!
[bird screeches]
Rosette is calling me.
[AZMARIA] She what?!
Did he tell you where
she was located?
She's waiting
in Central Park,
but Chrono said he
was going there alone.
If he manipulates the mobs,
it will be like San Francisco.
We need to go there as well.
Rosette...
[CHRONO gasps]
What an inelegant weapon.
But the Holy Woman wishes to
retrieve her life for herself.
So, I will merely be a
spectator, exactly like Him.
[CHRONO] Rosette...
if that's what you want,
go ahead and shoot.
If it's for you...
if it's so you can live,
I don't mind dying.
But please, before
you pull the trigger,
there's just one thing
I have to do before I die.
I have to settle things...
...with my own past.
[CHRONO yells]
Heh. Ah!
Chrono, you...!
How dare you!
Die, and repent!
Chrono...
Ahhh!
Rosette!
Rosette...
C-Chrono?
[CHRONO]
You know who I am!
Your heart's been freed
from Aion's spell.
But what was the cost...
...of that last stigmata?
Chrono... I...
Aghh!
So these are your horns?
Chrono!
I told you I was
going to design
the other ending
to the Apocalypse.
Your power's already
been surpassed.
Chrono!
Aaahhh!
Ai... on!
Chrono... Chrono... Chrono!
[weakly]
Don't do it, Rosette!
But I must.
I'll give it all to you, so that
you can fight him, Chrono.
If giving my life can
truly save a lot of people,
then it's all right if I die.
Even if this is just God's plan
to restore a corrupt world.
I'm the one that
will make the choice.
That is our greatest power.
That's the reason that
God granted us wisdom.
It's why he gave us hearts.
[CHRONO screams]
I understand now.
Aion!!!
[CHRONO] Now I see that
we need to be incomplete.
[AION] And making
you believe that
is just one of their tricks.
Chrono...
[AION yells]
Chrono!
Why hast thou forsaken...?
Aaagghh!
[weakly] Chrono...
[ANNA and MARY] Rosette!
[AZMARIA] Rosette?
[CLAIRE] Chrono!
[GIRLS] Rosette! Chrono! Chrono!
[REMINGTON gasps]
[REMINGTON sighs]
[AZMARIA] Father Remington...
This is all we could...
What of Rosette and Chrono?
[AZMARIA sobs]
[REMINGTON]
I see. So it's over.
[AZMARIA] No...
I-I believe that wherever
she is, Rosette's alive.
I'm sure of it.
[ROSETTE] I'm sure it
sounds like a cliché,
but I've always dreamed
of my own house.
[CHRONO] Your own house?
[ROSETTE] Mm-Hm.
A house on a grassy field.
I'd plant crops and tend sheep,
and sit by the fire at night.
[CHRONO] No matter where we go,
as long as I'm with you,
I've found my home.
[ROSETTE] It's the
last episode, "Chrono."
[CHRONO] Let's go back,
Rosette... to our home.