Sora: THAT FELINE IS OFF
TO FIND THE MISSING CHILD,
AND WE'RE STUCK HERE,
NOT KNOWING WHAT TO DO.
SOMEHOW WE HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO OPEN THAT GATE,
BUT HOW?
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
[ HOWLING ]
Myotismon has shut the gate.
You can't follow him now.
LISTEN, POPS, HELP US
GET THROUGH THAT GATE.
THE EIGHTH KID
IS DOOMED IF WE DON'T.
AND THAT ISN'T ALL.
IF THAT ROTTEN CREEP
GOES ON A RAMPAGE
IN THE REAL WORLD,
LOTS OF INNOCENT PEOPLE
WILL GET HURT.
THERE HAS TO BE SOME WAY
WE CAN OPEN THE GATE AGAIN.
Well, of course there is.
NO KIDDING?
HOW, THEN?
Any door can be opened
with the right keys.
OH, DON'T BE
SO MYSTERIOUS, GENNAI.
Follow me to my house,
and I will explain everything.
WHERE'S THAT?
Look above you.
WHAT KIND OF DIRECTIONS
ARE THOSE?
Very good ones
if you will just listen.
All: HUH?
Keep looking,
and you shall see it.
Tai: THERE --
A SEARCHLIGHT.
OH!
Sorry, I ran out of maps,
but follow the light.
You can't miss it.
EXCELLENT.
Snack time for me.
LET'S JET!
Joe: LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GOING
TO BE DOING A LITTLE SWIMMING.
MY HAT,
MY BEAUTIFUL HAT!
Matt: EITHER WE GOT
THOSE DIRECTIONS REALLY WRONG,
OR GENNAI'S HOUSE
IS IN A LAKE.
SO THAT'S WHY
I'VE NEVER FOUND IT.
MUST BE REALLY TOUGH
TO GET PIZZA DELIVERED.
HEY, COME ON IN.
THE WATER'S FINE.
OH, NO.
All: HUH?
OH.
Matt: OH.
T.K.: OOH.
Joe: WOW.
Tai: STEPS?
ALL RIGHT, GANG,
WE'RE IN BUSINESS.
THERE ARE STAIRS GOING DOWN
INTO THE LAKE.
Matt: THEY MUST LEAD
TO GENNAI'S HOUSE.
WELL, WHAT ARE WE
WAITING FOR?
Joe: I WAS HOPING HE'D SEND
A BOAT TO PICK US UP.
HMM.
HEY, WAIT FOR ME!
Mimi: IF ANYONE WANTS ANY SUSHI,
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE.
I WISH
I HAD MY BOOTS.
ME, TOO. LOOK.
QUITE A PLACE,
IF YOU DON'T MIND LIVING
IN PINK FOG.
NO LAWN TO MOW.
Tai: I DON'T
SEE A DOORBELL.
Matt: HEY, GENNAI.
Mimi: GENNAI.
WHO NEEDS A DOORBELL
WITH SUCH NOISY VISITORS?
IT'S THE REAL GENNAI.
WHO DID YOU EXPECT,
SANTA CLAUS?
WE'VE JUST NEVER
SEEN THE REAL YOU.
YEAH.
SO, TELL US, HOW COME
YOU'RE ALWAYS HIDING?
I'M NOT.
YOU COULD HAVE
COME IN PERSON,
BUT YOU ALWAYS
USED PROJECTIONS, RIGHT?
IT'S JUST A SHOW
TO IMPRESS YOU.
WHAT KIND OF A PERSON
ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
A HUMAN
OR SOME KIND OF DIGIMON?
THAT IS NOT IMPORTANT.
HOW COME YOU CALL US
THE DIGIDESTINED?
EASY. I'M OLD,
BUT I'M NOT DEAF.
YOU WERE CHOSEN
TO SAVE THIS WORLD AND YOUR OWN.
BUT JUST HOW WERE WE CHOSEN?
WHY US?
YEAH, WE ONLY SIGNED UP
FOR SUMMER CAMP.
THAT IS ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW
FOR NOW. COME INSIDE.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
IS TO RETURN TO YOUR WORLD
AND FIND THE EIGHTH CHILD.
THAT, AND MAYBE
HAVE A NICE BOWL OF SOUP
AND A TUNA SANDWICH.
Mimi:
LOOK AT THE FISH!
HA HA HA HA.
BUT THOSE ARE HALIBUT.
THEY'RE SALTWATER FISH.
YOU ARE RIGHT.
SO I HAVE
TO FEED THEM POPCORN
AND SALTY PRETZELS
AND TONS OF SALTED NUTS.
Joe: DO YOU THINK
HE'S PULLING OUR LEGS?
Tai: I HAVE NO IDEA.
NOW THE WEATHER.
STATE, COUNTY, CITY -- DOES
ANYONE RECOGNIZE THIS AREA?
OUR HOMETOWN?
MM-HMM, AND THE RED
FLASHING CIRCLE INDICATES...
MYOTISMON'S LOCATION.
MYOTISMON!
WOW, HE'S ONLY A MILE
FROM WHERE WE ALL LIVE.
I'M AFRAID SO.
I'LL BET YOU
THAT HE GOES DOWNTOWN.
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
WHAT DID YOU FIND?
NOTHING. CABLE'S FINE.
SO WHAT'S CAUSING
ALL THIS INTERFERENCE?
HA HA HA HA HA.
Tai: PLEASE TELL US HOW
TO OPEN THE GATE TO OUR WORLD.
YOU CERTAINLY ARE IMPATIENT.
KEEP YOUR GOGGLES ON,
MY YOUNG FRIEND.
YOU'LL NEED THESE.
CHECK 'EM OUT.
Matt: DIGIMON KEY CARDS.
Joe: IT'S
THE SPITTING IMAGE.
Tai: ALL RIGHT,
LOOK AT GOMAMON.
I'M CUTER IN PERSON.
Mimi: BUT WHAT
ARE THEY FOR?
YEAH, AND HOW DO THEY
HELP US OPEN THE GATE?
WELL, THERE ARE NINE HOLES
ON THE STONE WALL OF THE GATE.
HMM, YEAH, SO?
OH, WAIT.
DO THE CARDS GO
INTO THE HOLES?
THAT'S RIGHT. HOWEVER,
TAKE A CLOSER LOOK.
IT'S NOT QUITE AS SIMPLE
AS THAT.
DO YOU SEE THE PROBLEM?
Izzy: YOU'RE GIVING US
ONE TOO MANY CARDS.
THAT'S RIGHT. MM-HMM.
ONE OF THEM IS A FAKE.
All: OH.
WE'LL TRY THEM ALL
TILL WE GET
THE RIGHT COMBINATION.
NO, YOU WILL NOT,
YOU SILLY BOY.
THAT'S ABSOLUTELY
THE LAST THING YOU SHOULD DO.
THERE ARE MANY WORLDS.
IF YOU PUT THE CARDS
IN THE WRONG HOLES,
YOU COULD END UP
IN A DIFFERENT WORLD
WITH NO WAY TO RETURN.
AHEM. LET ME EXPLAIN.
THE WRONG CARDS MIGHT TAKE YOU
TO A WORLD WHERE, FOR EXAMPLE,
PEOPLE AND DIGIMON
SWITCH SKIN.
HA HA HA.
NO, NOT THAT!
I LIKE MY SKIN!
DON'T WORRY, DON'T WORRY.
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO SWITCH YOUR SKIN WITH ANYONE
AS LONG AS YOU LEARN HOW
TO USE THE CARDS CORRECTLY.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT TO DO.
YOU MUST LEARN
TO USE YOUR POWER
THE WAY
MYOTISMON IS USING HIS.
TOMORROW I'LL TEACH YOU
THE PROPER USE
OF THE CARDS.
[ SNORING ]
Izzy: THE DIGITAL WORLD
IS LIKE OUR WORLD,
BUT DIFFERENT.
WHY IS THAT?
Gennai: THE SAME MATERIAL
IS USED IN ALL WORLDS.
MOLECULES AND ATOMS?
EXACTLY. EVERYTHING HERE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD --
PLANTS, TREES, BUILDINGS,
EVEN THE DIGIMON THEMSELVES --
CAME FROM COMPUTER DATA
IN YOUR WORLD.
SO IF THERE
ARE STRANGE THINGS HERE,
THEY ARE THE RESULT
OF BROKEN OR MISSING DATA.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, GENNAI?
ARE YOU JUST MADE UP
OF COMPUTER DATA, TOO?
OF COURSE.
SO IN EACH OF THE WORLDS
I WOULD APPEAR
SOMEWHAT DIFFERENT.
BUT, GENNAI,
IF YOU'RE NOT HUMAN,
HOW ARE YOU DIFFERENT
FROM DIGIMON?
I HAVE NO ATTRIBUTES.
ATTRIBUTES?
JUST WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
YOU MEAN THE DIFFERENT ATTACKS
DIGIMON HAVE?
YES, AND THE WAY
A DIGIMON DIGEVOLVES,
BUT ATTRIBUTES
DETERMINE MUCH MORE THAN THAT.
THEY EXPLAIN
WHY SOME DIGIMON ARE GOOD
AND SOME ARE EVIL.
ALL DIGIMON CAN BE CLASSIFIED
AS DATA, VIRUS, OR VACCINE.
WE'RE DEFINITELY FAMILIAR
WITH THE VIRUS KIND.
BY THE WAY,
HAVE YOU USED
THAT DIGIMON ANALYZER
I GAVE YOU?
YES, BUT THERE IS SOMETHING
I WANTED TO ASK YOU ABOUT IT.
WHAT'S THAT?
I'M ONLY ABLE
TO ACCESS INFORMATION
ON DIGIMON
THAT I HAVE SEEN,
NOT ON THE ONES
THE OTHER KIDS HAVE SEEN.
HMM, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT IS A PROBLEM.
IS IT ONE
YOU CAN SOLVE?
JUST LEAVE IT TO ME,
MY YOUNG FRIEND.
I SHOULD HAVE IT
ALL TAKEN CARE OF
BY MORNING,
BUT FOR NOW,
YOU HAD BETTER
GET SOME REST.
OKAY.
Sora: WOW, JOE, WHY NOT
EAT THE BONES, TOO?
Joe: HEY,
I WAS HUNGRY.
All: HUH?
GOOD MORNING, ALL.
All: HI.
IZZY, I COMPLETED
THE MODIFICATIONS
FOR YOUR COMPUTER.
WHEN YOU INSERT
SOMEONE'S DIGIVICE
INTO THIS ADAPTER,
THE ANALYZER
WILL SHOW INFORMATION
ON ANY DIGIMON
THAT PERSON HAS SEEN.
I ALSO INSTALLED
A NEW SCREENSAVER.
YOU KNOW THE ONE
WITH FISHES SWIMMING AROUND?
I LIKE THAT ONE.
GREAT MINDS THINK ALIKE.
I HAVE A REQUEST
FOR ALL OF YOU.
DON'T FORGET
THAT YOU ARE THE DIGIDESTINED.
Joe: I'LL NEVER FORGET
THIS STOMACHACHE. OHH.
JOE, THIS IS SERIOUS.
I HAVE DONE ALL I CAN DO.
I CAN NO LONGER HELP ONCE YOU
RETURN TO MYOTISMON'S CASTLE.
GOOD LUCK.
Joe: MAN, THIS PLACE
LOOKS EVEN SCARIER
THAN IT DID
THE FIRST TIME.
[ GROWLING ]
HOW DO WE GET
PAST THE DEVIDRAMON?
I'LL TAKE THEM OUT
WHILE YOU GO IN.
Both: MM-HMM.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
TENTOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
KABUTERIMON!
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
KABUTERIMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
MEGAKABUTERIMON!
Izzy: LET'S GO.
NOW'S OUR CHANCE.
HORNBUSTER!
AAH! MOVE IT, MOVE IT!
[ GROANS ]
WELL, SO MUCH
FOR A QUIET ENTRANCE.
HORNBUSTER!
[ PANTING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
WHOA! AAH! OHH!
MUDIMON!
OH, WHAT HAPPENED,
IZZY?
EVERYTHING'S TURNED
ALL RIGHT SIDE UP AGAIN.
YOU FIXED THE WARP
IN SPACE.
Tai: COME ON.
LET'S GET TO THE GATE.
WE'VE GOT TO FIGURE OUT
THE PATTERN IN THESE CARDS.
WHAT, A CLUE?
GOOD ONE, BAD ONE,
FUNKY ONE.
MAYBE -- IN TRAINING,
ROOKIE, AND CHAMPION?
OR COULD IT JUST BE
SMALL ONE,
MEDIUM ONE, BIG ONE?
HOW CAN WE BE SURE?
WE DON'T HAVE A CLUE
WHICH CARD IS FAKE.
MAYBE IT'S WHERE THEY LIVE,
WATER OR LAND.
Mimi: MAYBE THE KEY
IS IN THEIR NAMES,
LIKE AGUMON
STARTS WITH "A."
THAT'S LETTER NUMBER ONE.
THEN --
NO, IT REALLY
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
IZZY, WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING AT?
Izzy: MYOTISMON USED A SPELL
TO OPEN THE GATE.
THIS PICTURE MUST HAVE
SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT.
SOME OF THESE CHARACTERS
I KNOW.
SAGITTARIUS AND LEO
ARE SIGNS OF THE ZODIAC,
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
ABOUT A MONKEY
IN ANY HOROSCOPE.
AND WHAT'S THIS STAR PATTERN?
[ RUMBLING ]
HMM?
MATT, WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, MAYBE SOMEBODY
SHOULD GO TAKE A LOOK.
I'LL GO FIND OUT.
WE HAVE
TO FIGURE OUT THE CARDS.
Joe: WHAT'S THE POINT?
WE'LL NEVER UNLOCK THE GATE.
Sora: DON'T SAY THAT.
EVEN IF THE CARDS
LOOK RIGHT,
WE HAVE NO WAY OF KNOWING
TILL IT'S TOO LATE.
WE HAVE TO TRY, JOE.
Tai: WE DON'T
HAVE MUCH TIME.
HEY, EVERYONE,
THE WALLS AND CEILINGS
IN THE CASTLE ARE CAVING IN.
THE PASSAGES ARE ALL BLOCKED.
Matt: WE CAN'T GO BACK.
WE'RE TRAPPED.
Izzy: NOW WE HAVE
TO OPEN THE GATE.
ONE OF US HAS
TO CHOOSE NINE CARDS
AND PUT THEM
IN THE HOLES.
YOU, TAI.
ME?
YEAH, IT'S YOUR CALL.
MINE? WHY IS IT
UP TO ME?
I'M NOT TRYING TO PUT YOU
ON THE SPOT OR ANYTHING.
I JUST THINK WE ALL
REALLY BELIEVE IN YOU, TAI.
ME?
JOE'S RIGHT.
IN TIMES LIKE THESE,
DECISIONS NEED TO BE MADE
BY THE ONE IN CHARGE.
HAVE YOU GUYS GONE CRAZY?
WHO MADE ME LEADER?
DO YOU REMEMBER
WHEN YOU WERE GONE, TAI?
WE FELL APART, AND AFTER THAT,
WEREN'T YOU THE ONE
WHO MANAGED TO BRING US ALL
BACK TOGETHER AGAIN?
UH, YEAH, I GUESS.
Mimi: DO IT, TAI!
MIMI.
I JUST WANT TO GET BACK
TO MY HOME.
THAT'S ALL.
OH, I'M SORRY.
I WAS BEING SELFISH AGAIN.
I HAVE TO REMEMBER
WE'RE A TEAM.
COME ON, TAI, SAVE THE DAY.
YEAH, WE HAVE TO BELIEVE
IN OUR FRIENDS.
REMEMBER WHAT GENNAI SAID?
Matt: HE SAID
TO BELIEVE IN OUR POWER.
YOU BELIEVE,
DON'T YOU, TAI?
Joe: WE'VE GONE THROUGH A LOT
OF WEIRD STUFF ALREADY.
IF WE
HADN'T STUCK TOGETHER,
WE NEVER WOULD HAVE
BEATEN CIDRAMON...
Mimi: OR ESCAPED
FROM TOY TOWN.
AND I'D STILL
BE MAKING FRENCH FRIES
IN VEGIMON'S DINER
IF YOU HADN'T SAVED ME.
All: YOU CAN DO IT, TAI.
ALL RIGHT.
[ GROWLING AND SNICKERING ]
YOU'RE LEAVING IT UP TO ME
TO GET THIS GATE OPEN, HUH?
AND WHATEVER I DECIDE,
YOU'RE WILLING TO GO WITH IT?
All: UH-HUH.
WELL, I'VE DECIDED
I WANT IZZY TO DO IT.
WHAT? YOU DO?
WHY ME?
IF THAT'S WHAT TAI THINKS,
I ACCEPT IT.
Matt: DON'T WORRY, IZZY.
TAI BELIEVES IN YOU,
AND SO DO THE REST OF US.
BUT WHAT HAPPENS
IF I'M WRONG?
Mimi: NO ONE
WILL BLAME YOU.
Joe: WE KNOW YOU'RE THE ONE
FOR THE JOB. GO FOR IT.
I STILL HAVE NO IDEA
HOW THIS ALL FITS TOGETHER.
Gabumon: YOU COULD USE YOUR
COMPUTER TO FIGURE IT OUT.
THE COMPUTER?
RIGHT NOW, I'D RATHER USE IT
TO LOG ONTO THE INTERNET
AND BOOK US A FLIGHT
OUT OF THIS PLACE.
HUH?
WAIT A MINUTE.
THE HORSE, THE LION,
AND THEN...
THE MONKEY. THAT'S IT.
REMEMBER, ALL DIGIMON
CAN BE CLASSIFIED
AS DATA, VIRUS,
OR VACCINE.
COULD IT BE?
WHO HERE HAS MET UP
WITH DIGITOMOMON AND GECKOMON?
Joe: I HAVE.
GIVE ME YOUR DIGIVICE.
PRODIGIOUS!
YOU FIGURED IT OUT?
I MIGHT HAVE.
COME ON, GUYS.
CHECK THIS OUT.
THE FIRST THREE --
THE LION, THE ARCHER,
AND THE MONKEY --
WOULD BE LEOMON, CENTAURUMON,
AND ETEMON.
IN ADDITION, THERE'S ONE
OF EACH CLASSIFICATION --
DATA, VIRUS, AND VACCINE.
THE STARS,
STARTING AT THE TOP,
REPRESENT IN TRAINING,
ROOKIE, AND CHAMPION.
SO NOW WE CAN PUT ALL THE CARDS
IN THE RIGHT SQUARES.
Sora: YOU DID IT, IZZY.
GOOD WORK.
WE KNEW
YOU'D FIGURE IT OUT.
NOT SO FAST.
THERE ARE TWO CARDS HERE.
ONE OF THEM IS THE FAKE,
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHICH ONE.
SO THAT'S IT. I'M SORRY.
WE STILL CAN'T BE CERTAIN
WHERE THE GATE WILL OPEN TO.
BUT WE MADE IT
THIS FAR.
THAT'S GREAT.
YES, IT IS.
TAI CAN PICK
WHICH ONE'S FAKE.
IF I CAN'T,
EVERYONE GETS AN ICE CREAM,
AND I'M BUYING.
HUH?
All: HUH?
AAH!
Tai: WHAT IS THAT?
I'LL TELL YOU
IN A MINUTE.
IT'S DOKUGUMON,
AN EVIL DIGIMON
WITH COMPUTER VIRUS PARASITES
COVERING HIS BODY.
INTRUDERS IN THE CASTLE
MUST BE DESTROYED!
GO GET THEM! HA HA!
[ SCREAMING ]
GOMAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
IKKAKUMON!
PALMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
TOGEMON!
GABUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GARURUMON!
BLUE BLASTER!
HURRY, HURRY, HURRY!
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
NEEDLE SPRAY!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
OH! AAH!
OH, OH!
YOKOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
BIYOMON!
SPIRAL TWISTER!
Tai: I CAN'T DECIDE.
WHICH ONE IS THE FAKE CARD?
HURRY UP, CHOOSE.
IF I CHOOSE WRONG,
WE'RE TOAST.
[ GROWLS ]
POISON THREAD!
AAH!
OHH!
All: OHH!
POISON COBWEB!
[ GROANING ]
HA HA HA HA HA.
GARURUMON!
DIGEVOLVE AGAIN!
[ GROWLS ]
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
GARURUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
WEREGARURUMON! [ Howls ]
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ MONSTER FRIENDS
TO THE BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
Matt: TAI,
MAKE UP YOUR MIND NOW.
WE'RE OUT OF TIME!
OKAY, IT'S THIS ONE.
COME ON, NOW!
♪ HEY, DIGIMON ♪
COME ON!
♪ CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
Tai: YOU'RE THE ONE, GOMAMON.
OPEN THE GATE!
IT'S OPENING.
IT WORKED.
COME ON!
LEAVE HIM
AND COME ON!
YOU'LL NEVER GET OUT OF HERE
IN ONE PIECE!
WOLF CLAW!
AAH!
THAT WAS REAL CLOSE,
SUNOMAN,
BUT IT LOOKS
LIKE WE MADE IT.
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GROANS ]
WHERE ARE WE?
I KNOW THIS PLACE.
THIS IS THE SUMMER CAMP
WHERE WE ALL MET.
YOU DID IT, TAI.
WE'RE HOME AGAIN.
OH, OH!
WE'RE BACK TO WHERE
WE WERE FIRST SUCKED
INTO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
BUT WHERE
ARE OUR DIGIMON?
I WONDER IF WE
GOT THE CARDS WRONG AFTER ALL.
THEN IN THIS WORLD,
WE COULD BE WITHOUT THEM.
Gabumon: YOU CAN'T GET RID
OF US THAT EASILY.
HA HA HA.
WAKE UP.
COME ON, SLEEPYHEADS.
Tai: WE'RE UP, WE'RE UP.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
WE THOUGHT WE OUGHT
TO GO LOOK FOR LUNCH.
NOW THAT WE'RE HOME,
WE DON'T HAVE
TO EAT LEAVES ANYMORE.
WE CAN EAT CHEESEBURGERS.
THAT'S RIGHT,
AND PEPPERONI PIZZA.
T.K.: AND FRENCH FRIES.
Sora: YEAH, AND BROCCOLI.
All: BROCCOLI?
HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT MY CARD
WAS THE FAKE, TAI?
I DIDN'T. I KEPT YOUR CARD
BECAUSE YOU'RE MY FRIEND.
HA HA.
THAT'S SO NICE.
HEY, EVERYBODY.
WE'VE GOT
TO FIND THE EIGHTH CHILD.
GET A MOVE ON.
MYOTISMON'S THERE
AHEAD OF US.
I'M HAPPY THAT WE'RE FINALLY
HEADED BACK TO MY HOMETOWN,
AND WE ALREADY KNOW
THAT'S WHERE WE'RE GOING
TO FIND THE EIGHTH CHILD.
LET'S GO!