Matt: METALSEADRAMON
HAD FOLLOWED US
FROM THE UNDERWATER CHANNELS
AND WAS NOW IN A FIERCE BATTLE
WITH OUR DIGIS.
IN THE MIDST OF ALL OF IT,
HE RELEASED HIS RIVER OF POWER
AND HIT WHAMON
WITH A DEVASTATING BLAST.
WARGREYMON HAD NO OTHER CHOICE
BUT TO USE HIS TERRAFORCE
TO FINALLY PUT AN END
TO METALSEADRAMON.
SADLY, OUR FRIEND WHAMON
WAS RECONFIGURED AS WELL.
AS THE OCEAN
STARTED TO DISAPPEAR,
WE TOOK IT AS A SIGN
THAT THINGS
MIGHT GET BACK TO NORMAL.
THE ODDS OF THAT HAPPENING
ANYTIME SOON -- NOT GOOD.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Joe: MATT! HEY, MATT!
Sora: MATT, WHERE ARE YOU?
I'M WORRIED.
WHAT COULD HAVE
HAPPENED TO HIM, TAI?
MATT'S A BIG BOY.
HE CAN TAKE CARE OF HIMSELF.
WELL, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT IF HE WAS
KIDNAPPED BY PUPPETMON?
YEAH, OR
SOMETHING WORSE.
NO, IT WASN'T
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
All: HUH?
Tai: HOW
DO YOU KNOW?
COME ON, LET'S GO.
Tai: WHAT? HE JUST
WALKED AWAY,
AND YOU DIDN'T EVEN
TRY TO STOP HIM?
WELL, NO.
WAS I SUPPOSED TO?
I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO GO
USE THE BUSHES OR SOMETHING.
HUH. THIS IS WEIRD.
IT'S ONE THING
IF HE WAS KIDNAPPED,
BUT WHY WOULD HE
DISAPPEAR LIKE THIS?
HE'S BEEN GONE TOO LONG
FOR JUST A POTTY BREAK.
WAIT A MINUTE.
HAS MATT BEEN
KIND OF STRANGE LATELY?
Izzy: HE HAS BEEN
ACTING HIGH-STRUNG.
AAH!
REMEMBER WHEN GABUMON HAD
THAT DIGEVOLVING PROBLEM?
YEAH, I BET
THERE'S A CONNECTION.
KARI, WHAT IS IT?
I THOUGHT I HEARD A VOICE.
WAS IT MATT'S?
I DON'T HEAR ANYTHING.
COME ON, KARI, DON'T
YOU START LOSING IT, TOO.
HE COULDN'T BE FAR AWAY.
WE SHOULD LOOK FOR HIM.
YEAH, I SUPPOSE.
OKAY, GUYS, LET'S GO.
GATOMON, IT WASN'T
MATT'S VOICE I HEARD.
WHOSE WAS IT?
Gabumon: MATT, COME ON.
I'M ALL FOR EXERCISE,
BUT I'M NOT BUILT
FOR LONG DISTANCES.
MATT, WHERE ARE WE GOING?
JUST AWAY.
I NEED SOME SPACE.
Puppetmon: HA HA HA!
OH, THE POOR LITTLE KID
NEEDS A LITTLE SPACE,
FAR AWAY FROM HIS LITTLE
FRIENDS AND CLOSER TO ME.
Cherrymon:
I AGREE COMPLETELY.
I'M NOT WAITING. I'LL
PUT HIM OUT OF HIS MISERY.
THOSE DIGIDESTINED KIDS
REALLY BUG ME.
WAIT A MINUTE, PUPPETMON.
I HAVE A BETTER IDEA.
YOU CAN TAKE CARE OF THOSE
OTHER DIGIDESTINED CHILDREN,
BUT AS FOR THIS ONE,
LEAVE HIM TO ME.
I'LL HAVE HIM CLIMBING UP A TREE
BEFORE I'M THROUGH WITH HIM.
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
YOU EVER FELT LIKE
A FIFTH WHEEL, GABUMON?
THAT'S WHAT I FEEL LIKE.
ALL THIS TIME,
I THOUGHT I HAD,
LIKE, A PURPOSE,
YOU KNOW?
TO LOOK OUT
FOR MY LITTLE BROTHER.
I THOUGHT T.K. WOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO SURVIVE
WITHOUT ME
WATCHING OVER HIM.
BUT SUDDENLY,
IT'S LIKE HE'S GROWING UP.
HE DOESN'T NEED ME ANYMORE.
OH, AND IT'S NOT JUST HIM.
IT'S EVERYBODY, MAN.
WHEN I THINK OF TAI AND MIMI
AND SORA AND THE OTHERS,
THIS PLACE HAS CHANGED THEM
FOR THE BETTER.
THEY'RE STRONGER NOW.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE THEY'VE
DIGEVOLVED OR SOMETHING.
BUT YOU SEE,
THE PROBLEM IS I HAVEN'T.
I'M STILL STUCK
IN THE SAME PLACE.
I HAVEN'T CHANGED A BIT.
YOU MAY NOT SEE IT, MATT,
BUT YOU'VE CHANGED A LOT.
OH, PLEASE, GABUMON,
GIVE ME A BREAK.
I'M THE SAME JERK
I ALWAYS WAS.
HEY, COME ON.
IT'LL NEVER HAPPEN --
NOT THIS WAY.
I'VE FINALLY GOT IT
FIGURED OUT.
IF I'M EVER GOING TO CHANGE,
I HAVE TO DO IT ON MY OWN.
ON MY OWN.
THE OTHERS CAN'T HELP ME.
Cherrymon:
WELL, WELL, WELL.
LOOK WHAT WE'VE GOT HERE.
GREETINGS, NATURE LOVERS.
WHAT -- YOU MEAN YOU'VE NEVER
SEEN A TALKING TREE?
NOT MANY.
BE CAREFUL. THAT'S CHERRYMON,
LORD OF THE FOREST
AND THE BEST REASON
FOR THE EXISTENCE OF TERMITES.
STOP RIGHT THERE, OR I'LL
TURN YOU INTO TOOTHPICKS.
YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T
BE THAT RUDE.
CALM DOWN. MY FIGHTING
DAYS ARE OVER.
I ONLY WANT TO TALK WITH YOU.
IN FACT, YOU MIGHT EVEN SAY
I'VE TURNED OVER A NEW LEAF.
HA HA HA HA!
Izzy: OH,
IT'S NO USE.
I'M GETTING NOTHING.
FOR SOME REASON,
THE DIGEVICES AREN'T
WORKING IN THIS FOREST.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT SO SURE WE
SHOULD BE TRYING TO FIND HIM.
EVERYONE NEEDS
TO BE ALONE SOMETIMES.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET HIM
BREAK UP THIS TEAM.
WE'RE GOING TO FIND HIM.
WE'RE ALWAYS WALKING AROUND,
SEARCHING FOR SOMEONE.
I'VE NEVER DONE
SO MUCH WALKING.
YEAH, IT'S DISGUSTING.
MY CALVES ARE STARTING
TO LOOK LIKE A BODYBUILDER'S.
LIKE A WHAT?
OH, MIMI.
Puppetmon: YOO-HOO!
Sora: HUH?
Tai: PUPPETMON?
HI, EVERYBODY!
HEY, T.K.,
DID YOU MISS ME?
NO, AND I'M NOT GOING TO PLAY
WITH YOU ANYMORE, EITHER!
NO?
WELL, FINE.
YOU'RE NOT
A LOT OF FUN, ANYWAY.
FRONT AND CENTER, EVERYBODY!
YES, SIR!
Sora: UH-OH!
GARBAGEMON!
THEY'RE AS TOUGH
AS THEY ARE MEAN.
AND THEY DON'T
SMELL VERY GOOD, EITHER.
JUNK-CHUCKERS --
READY, AIM, FIRE!
All: AAH!
All: RUN!
MIMI!
HMM.
I WON'T BUDGE!
LET'S LET THEM
DO THE RUNNING FOR A CHANGE!
HUH?
HMM?
MIMI, COME ON!
I MUST BE NUTS!
I TOUCHED THAT STUFF!
NO OFFENSE, BUT EVEN
IF I FELT LIKE TALKING,
IT WOULDN'T BE TO A TREE.
SEE YOU AROUND.
HEY, WHAT'S THE IDEA?
YOUNG MAN, DIDN'T
ANYONE EVER TELL YOU
YOU SHOULD LISTEN
TO YOUR ELDERS?
OR WAS IT REDWOODS?
I CAN NEVER QUITE
GET THOSE TWO STRAIGHT.
BUT ANYWAY, I DIGRESS.
SO, YOU'RE STILL STUCK
IN THE SAME PLACE.
STILL THE SAME OLD JERK
YOU ALWAYS WERE.
SURPRISED, HUH?
I KNOW ALL ABOUT IT.
MUST BE TOUGH
BEING IN SUCH A RUT.
YOU'VE BEEN
SPYING ON ME, HUH?
HA HA HA HA!
I DON'T NEED TO SPY,
BECAUSE NOTHING
HAPPENS IN THIS FOREST
THAT I DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
IF YOU'RE SO SMART,
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
TELL ME THAT.
AH, AS SIMPLE
AS THAT, EH?
KIDS. YOU WANT ALL THE ANSWERS
JUST HANDED TO YOU
ON A MAHOGANY PLATTER.
BUT YOU NEVER WANT
TO DO THE HARD WORK
OF LOOKING DEEP WITHIN YOURSELF,
WHERE ALL THE ANSWERS TRULY LIE.
LET'S GO.
DON'T YOU LISTEN TO THAT
TALKING FIREWOOD, MATT.
COME ON!
THAT'S RIGHT. GO ON.
BUT YOU'LL NEVER
LEARN HOW TO CHANGE.
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE
WHAT YOU ARE RIGHT NOW.
I WANT TO CHANGE.
YES, BUT ARE YOU
REALLY READY?
CHANGE ISN'T ALWAYS
A PLEASANT THING.
YOU MIGHT FIND OUT THINGS
THAT YOU WISH YOU HADN'T.
I'M READY.
MORE THAN READY.
ENOUGH TALKING, BIG GUY!
IF YOU'VE GOT SOME
ANSWERS, LET'S SEE THEM!
[ Thinking ] HA HA!
HE FELL FOR IT
LIKE AN OVERRIPE FIG.
ALL RIGHT, KID,
I'LL HELP YOU OUT.
FIRST OFF, YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO DEFEAT YOUR RIVAL.
MY RIVAL?
THERE.
IN THAT LAKE, YOU WILL
SEE THE FACE OF THE ONE
WHO IS PREVENTING YOU
FROM BECOMING AS STRONG
AS YOU COULD BE.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I KNOW IT SOUNDS PRETTY BOGUS,
BUT MIGHT AS WELL LOOK.
LISTEN, MATT!
YOU DON'T REALLY
BELIEVE HIM, DO YOU?
[ GASPS ]
TAI? COME ON!
WHAT KIND OF TRICK IS THIS?
[ PANTING ]
HA! DON'T YOU KNOW
THAT WHEREVER YOU GO,
THERE WILL ALWAYS
BE GARBAGE?
OKAY, READY, GUYS?
MAKE A MESS!
AAH!
GRR!
YEAH!
HAH!
METEOR WING!
ELECTRO SHOCKER!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
GANGWAY
FOR NEEDLE SPRAY!
NOVA BLAST!
WAY TO GO!
Joe: THAT TRASH
IS THRASHED!
HA HA HA!
GREAT! YOU'VE TOTALLY
RUINED MY GARBAGE FUN.
I'M BEATEN!
I'M GOING HOME!
PSYCHE!
LOOK BEHIND YOU!
IT'S TRASH!
LOOK OUT!
HERE'S MUD IN YOUR EYE!
OH, NO! HELP!
JUNK-CHUCKER!
NIGHTMARE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
TOGEMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
LILLYMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
OH!
TWICE AS NICE!
TRASH THAT PETUNIA!
THAT CHICK IS HEAVIER
THAN SHE LOOKS.
FLOWER CANNON!
AAH!
ALL RIGHT!
FINISH THEM OFF!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
GREYMON DIGEVOLVE
TO METAL GREYMON!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
GIGABLASTER!
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ MONSTER FRIENDS
TO THE BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
Cherrymon: BEHOLD
THE FACE OF YOUR RIVAL.
SO, YOU'RE SAYING
I HAVE TO FIGHT TAI.
IS THAT IT?
NICE TRY, FOLIAGE-FACE.
YOU HAD ME GOING,
BUT YOU'LL HAVE
TO DO BETTER THAN THAT.
I HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH THAT.
THE LAKE
OF TRUTH REFLECTS
ONLY WHAT IS
IN A PERSON'S HEART --
HENCE THE NAME.
YOU'VE GOT
TO BE KIDDING.
SORRY, KID,
IT'S NEVER WRONG.
WELL, I'VE GOT
NEWS FOR YOU.
IT'S OFF THIS TIME.
WAY OFF.
YOU CAN ARGUE WITH ME
ALL YOU WANT,
BUT YOU'RE REALLY
ONLY ARGUING WITH YOURSELF.
HUH.
IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU FACED THE TRUTH.
THE ONE YOU CALL TAI
IS YOUR LEADER.
EVERYTHING HE SAYS, YOU DO.
YET, IN YOUR HEART,
YOU RESENT IT,
BECAUSE YOU'RE AS QUALIFIED
TO BE THE BOSS AS HE IS.
UNH!
STOP IT!
WHO DO YOU
THINK YOU ARE, HUH?
WHO DIED AND LEFT YOU
IN CHARGE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I'VE JUST ABOUT HAD IT.
Cherrymon: DO NOT BE ASHAMED
OF YOUR RESENTMENT.
DO NOT HIDE IT --
EMBRACE IT,
FOR IN YOUR ANGER
LIES YOUR STRENGTH.
ONLY WHEN YOU RECOGNIZE THAT
WILL YOU AT LAST
BE FREE TO GROW --
TO CHANGE.
SO FACE YOUR RIVAL,
AND PROVE YOU ARE
HIS EQUAL OR BETTER
BY DEFEATING HIM.
DON'T LISTEN.
HE'S JUST TRYING
TO CAUSE TROUBLE.
HE'S PLAYING GAMES
WITH YOUR MIND.
IT'S ALL PART
OF SOME KIND OF TRAP.
TAI IS YOUR FRIEND.
HE'S MY FRIEND, YEAH.
HE MAY NOT ALWAYS
ACT LIKE IT, BUT --
HE'S RIGHT.
TAI IS MY FRIEND.
YOU DON'T FIGHT
YOUR FRIENDS.
FRIEND? HA!
NOW THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
YOU DON'T EVEN BELIEVE
THAT SUCH A THING
REALLY EXISTS --
NOT IN YOUR HEART
OF HEARTS, ANYWAY.
HA HA HA HA HA!
HIT THE NAIL
ONE THE HEAD, DIDN'T I?
WHAT'S HE MEAN?
FRIENDSHIP,
LOYALTY, COMRADES --
FINE-SOUNDING WORDS,
BUT THAT'S ALL THEY ARE --
WORDS, DELUSIONS.
AND YOU'RE WISE ENOUGH
TO SEE THAT NOW.
YOU KNOW THAT ULTIMATELY
THE ONLY PERSON
YOU CAN DEPEND ON
IS YOURSELF.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, MATT?
HE'S WRONG, ISN'T HE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I-I DON'T KNOW.
YOU DON'T?
ALL RIGHT THEN.
THAT'S ENOUGH
MOPING AROUND FOR NOW.
LOOK, KID, STOP STARING
AT YOUR SHOES.
THE CHOICE IN FRONT OF YOU
IS SIMPLE.
IF YOU TRULY WANT TO CHANGE
TO REACH YOUR FULL POTENTIAL,
YOU MUST DEFEAT TAI.
IT'S EITHER THAT
OR BE CONTENT
TO BE LIVE YOUR LIFE
FOLLOWING IN THE SHADOWS
OF HIM FOREVER.
WHAT A CHOICE.
WHAT DO I DO?
OH, WHAT DO I DO?
[ SOBBING ]
OH, THAT'S A LAUGH.
WOULDN'T YOU KNOW
THAT MY CREST
HAD TO BE THE CREST
OF FRIENDSHIP?
MATT, THERE'S ONE THING
HE'S RIGHT ABOUT.
WHATEVER YOU'RE GOING
TO DO, DO IT.
BUT DO WHAT?
YOU'VE GOT TO HEAR
WHAT YOUR OWN CONSCIENCE
IS TELLING YOU
AND NOT LISTEN
TO ANYBODY ELSE --
NOT TAI
OR CHERRYMON OR ME.
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE
FAITH IN YOURSELF.
WHAT IF I MAKE
THE WRONG DECISION?
I KNOW THAT WHATEVER IT IS,
IT WILL BE THE RIGHT ONE,
BECAUSE I HAVE FAITH IN YOU,
AND WHICHEVER PATH YOU TAKE,
I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU.
YOU MEAN THAT?
MM-HMM.
YOU DO HAVE A FRIEND.
NEVER FORGET THAT.
I'LL ALWAYS BE THERE,
MATT, NO MATTER WHAT.
GABUMON.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
GABUMON
WARP-DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ WARP-DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
METALGARURUMON!
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
READY. LEAD THE WAY.
RIGHT.
HA HA HA HA HA!
YEAH, I THINK
THAT WENT RATHER WELL.
STILL, I'M SURPRISED
BY THE STRENGTH
OF THE BOND BETWEEN THEM.
IT TOOK EVERY TRICK I HAD
TO UNDERMINE IT.
IF PUPPETMON ISN'T CAREFUL,
THIS GAME COULD STILL BE LOST.
I MEANT
WHAT I SAID, MATT.
CHERRYMON WAS WRONG.
FRIENDSHIP, LOYALTY --
THEY'RE MORE
THAN JUST WORDS.
THEY'RE REAL,
AND THEY MATTER.
I'M GOING
TO PROVE IT TO YOU.
YUCK! SPLATTERING ME
WITH THEIR GUNK.
THOSE BUCKET BRAINS
WILL PAY FOR THIS.
THERE YOU ARE.
THE PLAN WENT PERFECTLY,
JUST AS I THOUGHT.
PLAN? WHAT PLAN?
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN IT.
I PLAYED THAT TRUSTING SAP
LIKE A VIOLIN.
HE'S GOING TO DO
OUR DIRTY WORK FOR US.
WELL, SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
ANY SECOND NOW,
WE'LL HEAR THE SOUNDS
OF WARGREYMON
AND METALGARURUMON
LOCKED IN MORTAL COMBAT.
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
OH, YEAH. WITH ANY LUCK,
THEY'LL DESTROY EACH OTHER.
WITH THE TWO STRONGEST
DIGIMON OUT OF THE WAY,
THE REST WILL FALL
LIKE ROTTEN FRUIT.
MORTAL COMBAT?
THIS I'VE GOT TO SEE.
LET'S GO.
WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
WAIT A MINUTE.
WE GOT TO BE CAREFUL.
THE DIGIDESTINED ARE STRONG,
STRONGER THAN I SUSPECTED,
AND TO UNDERESTIMATE THEM
COULD BE DISASTROUS.
WHAT? ARE YOU SAYING
I MIGHT LOSE?
I'M ONLY SAYING
THAT I THINK
YOU SHOULD
TAKE THEM SERIOUSLY.
THERE'S SOMETHING
ABOUT THEM.
SOMETHING?
HMM, YOU MEAN LIKE SOMETHING
I MIGHT BE MISSING?
WELL, NOT TOTALLY.
I HAVE EVERYTHING I NEED
TO TAKE CARE OF YOU!
PUPPET PUMMEL!
OH, THE HORROR!
HUH? MAN, THAT KIND
OF NEGATIVE ATTITUDE
REALLY BRINGS ME DOWN.
OKAY, OKAY,
I KNOW WHEN I'M BEAT!
YOU WIN! I SURRENDER!
JUST KIDDING!
HA HA HA HA HA!
TRASH DAY!
EVERYBODY IN THE CAN.
IF YOU'RE LUCKY,
YOU'LL GET RECYCLED.
All: NO!
THIS NASTY LITTLE CREEP'S
REALLY STARTING TO GET
ON MY NERVES.
TAI, HELP ME!
KARI!
KARI -- NO!
HA HA HA HA!
Metalgarurumon:
ICE WOLF CLAW!
AAH!
IT'S METALGARURUMON.
Joe: MATT!
MATT!
MATT, YOU'RE BACK!
BETTER LATE THAN NEVER.
WHERE YOU BEEN, BUDDY?
THANKS FOR SAVING
OUR NECKS,
BUT DID YOU HAVE
TO CUT IT THAT CLOSE?
AAH!
HUH? WHAT'S HE DOING?
HEY, WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT'S A CHALLENGE.
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO DIGEVOLVE, AND FAST.
WHAT HAVE BEEN EATING
OUT THERE IN THE FOREST?
YOU WANT TO FIGHT ME?
THIS IS INSANE.
IS THIS SOME KIND OF JOKE?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE'S DOING,
BUT CALL HIM OFF NOW.
NO, TAI, I WON'T.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
YOU WON'T?
I'M WARNING YOU.
HURRY UP AND DIGEVOLVE
INTO WARGREYMON,
BECAUSE I WON'T MISS
NEXT TIME.
I THINK
HE REALLY MEANS IT.
WELL, TIME'S
RUNNING OUT, AGUMON.
TAI, STOP HIM!
WISH I COULD, BUT THERE'S
ONLY ONE PERSON
WHO CAN STOP HIM.
WILL MATT SUCCEED
IN DESTROYING THE DIGIDESTINED
FROM WITHIN?
FIND OUT NEXT TIME
ON "DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS."