AFTER REACHING
THE CONTINENT OF SERVER,
WE FOUND A KOROMON VILLAGE,
BUT IT WAS OCCUPIED
BY THE PAGUMON.
LATER, DURING DINNER,
POYOMON DIGIVOLVED TO TOKUMON.
THAT NIGHT, LITTLE TOKO
WAS TAKEN FROM OUR CAMPSITE.
AGUMON FINALLY FOUND HIM
AND ALL THE KORUMON IN A CAVE.
THEY WERE BEING GUARDED
BY THE GAJIMON,
WHO WERE PLANNING ON GIVING US
TO THEIR LEADER,
THAT ROCK AND ROLL
DIGIJERK, ETEMON.
HE USED HIS MUSIC
LIKE A WEAPON
AND TRIED TO DESTROY
THE VILLAGE.
WE FOUND THE CREST
FOR TAI'S TAG,
AND IT CREATED
AN ESCAPE FORCE.
NEVER A DULL MOMENT!
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
FOX KIDS WORLDWIDE AND
THE U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGI ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE
THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Mimi: HOW FAR DO WE
HAVE TO WALK?
UNTIL EDOMON CAN'T FOLLOW US
ANYMORE
I DON'T THINK
THERE IS SUCH A PLACE!
Matt: WE CERTAINLY
CAN'T STOP HERE IN
THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
FOR ONE THING, IF WE
WERE ATTACKED, THERE'D
BE NO PLACE TO RUN TO.
[THINKING]
THIS IS STARTING
TO LOOK BAD.
EVERYONE'S BECOMING
SO TIMID AND AFRAID.
HEY, COME ON, YOU GUYS!
WHY'D WE STOP?
WHY'S EVERYONE SO SCARED?
AFTER ALL, WE DO
HAVE THE CREST, YOU KNOW.
THAT'S TRUE.
BUT DO WE REALLY KNOW
THE CREST WILL HELP
AGUMON TO DIGIVOLVE?
OF COURSE.
RIGHT, AGUMON?
HMM?
LISTEN, BUDDY,
THIS IS YOUR BIG CHANCE.
DON'T LET ME DOWN.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
THAT CAN DIGIVOLVE FURTHER,
SO EITHER YOU TRY
TO GET TO THE NEXT LEVEL
AND SAVE US FROM ETEMON,
OR I'LL GET A NEW DIGIMON!
[WHIMPERS]
NOT MUCH OF A CHOICE!
ARGH!
BY THE WAY,
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO USE
THE CREST TO DIGIVOLVE AGAIN?
WELL, FROM WHAT
WE'VE SEEN SO FAR
WITH THE OTHER
DIGIVOLUTIONS,
IT TAKES
A LOT OF ENERGY.
FOR EXAMPLE,
THEY CAN'T DIGIVOLVE
IF THEY'RE HUNGRY.
IN ADDITION,
THE PARTNER
OF THE DIGIMON
MUST BE IN SOME
SORT OF DANGER.
LIKE BEING UNDER
ATTACK OR SOMETHING.
BUT SINCE IT'S A HIGHER
LEVEL OF DIGIVOLVING,
MY THEORY IS EVEN MORE
ENERGY IS NEEDED.
SO WE'LL PROVIDE THE FOOD,
AND ETEMON WILL PROVIDE
THE DANGER. [LAUGHS]
YOU'D BETTER WATCH OUT,
YOU DIGIDESCENT KIDS,
I'LL FIND YOU,
AND WHEN I DO, YOU'LL WISH
YOU'D NEVER CROSSED ETEMON!
I'LL GET YOU!
AAH...HEY, NO MORE!
JUST ONE MORE
TEENSY BITE!
OHH!
READY FOR
THE SECOND COURSE?
BRGGGH.
OH, STOP
YOUR BELLYACHING
AND OPEN WIDE!
YOU'VE GOTTA
KEEP ON EATING!
EVERYONE'S
GIVING YOU THEIR FOOD
SO YOU CAN DIGIVOLVE.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
YEAH.
Mimi: WE DIDN'T GIVE HIM
OUR FOOD. HE TOOK IT.
OF ALL THE NERVE!
THE FOOD WON'T
DO US ANY GOOD.
WE STILL
CAN'T DIGIVOLVE.
THOSE OF US
WHO DON'T WORK,
DON'T EAT, HUH?
BUT I'M HUNGRY!
Tai: HEY, I CAN'T HEAR YOU,
I SAID, "IS THAT RIGHT?"
All: THAT'S RIGHT!
THAT'S WHY YOU
GOTTA TRY YOUR BEST
TO PROTECT EVERYBODY!
NOW, COME ON, BUDDY,
KEEP EATING!
I GUESS THERE'S NOT
MUCH ELSE WE CAN DO
TO HELP.
I DON'T KNOW IF
AGUMON CAN TAKE
MUCH MORE.
YEAH, TAI IS
REALLY PUSHING HIM.
AGUMON'S STUFFED LIKE
A THANKSGIVING TURKEY.
EAT UP!
YOU NEED THAT ENERGY!
TAI'S PERSONALITY
HAS TAKEN A TURN
FOR THE WORSE.
I REMEMBER HIM
BEING FRIENDLIER,
EVEN TO US
YOUNGER KIDS.
ACTUALLY, NOW THAT
YOU MENTION IT,
HE WAS COOL
DURING SOCCER CAMP.
TAI, PASS IT TO ME!
I'M OPEN!
NOW'S MY CHANCE TO SHOOT!
HERE I GO!
YEAH...UGH!
OOF!
AAHH...
NICE PASS, TAI!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
TAKING THE SHOT YOURSELF.
REMEMBER, THERE'S
NO "I" IN TEAM! HA HA!
TAI MIGHT LOOK LIKE
HE'S TRYING TO RUN THINGS
ALL BY HIMSELF,
BUT WHATEVER CRAZY ACTION
HE TAKES, HE DOES IT
FOR THE GOOD OF THE TEAM.
MM-HMM.
BUT NOW ALL THIS...
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO CAN HELP NOW!
SO YOU GOTTA
KEEP EATING, OK?
UGH, I CAN'T.
TAI'S PERSONALITY
SEEMS TO HAVE CHANGED
EVER SINCE HE GOT
THAT CREST OF COURAGE.
BOY, I'M HUNGRY.
HMM? HEY, GUYS!
MY TAG IS GLOWING!
IT MUST BE
REACTING TO SOMETHING!
Izzy: THE CREST
MUST BE NEARBY!
Tai: YOU THINK SO?
HEY, LOOK!
THERE'S SOMETHING
OUT THERE!
IT LOOKS LIKE
A BIG BUILDING
OR SOMETHING.
THAT MUST BE
WHERE MY CREST IS!
WHOA!
WHAT'S A CABLE DOING
OUT IN THE MIDDLE
OF NOWHERE?
WHOA!
WHAT IS IT,
LORD ETEMON?
AHA! SOMETHING'S CAUGHT
IN MY NETWORK! [LAUGHS]
THE INTRUDER'S
IN THE L-7 SECTOR.
LET'S SEE, L-7...
HOW'S THIS THING WORK?
OH, HERE IT IS.
WHERE IS IT?
[LAUGHS] IT'S NEAR
THE COLISEUM!
THAT'S WHERE
I HOLD MY ANNUAL
"TRIBUTE TO ME" SHOW.
I WONDER WHAT THEY'RE DOING
ALL THE WAY OVER THERE.
YOU GOT ANY IDEA?
MAYBE THEY WANNA
GET GOOD SEATS, BOSS.
OH, THEY'LL HAVE
A PERFECT VIEW
FOR THE SURPRISE SHOW
I'M PLANNING FOR THEM.
[LAUGHS]
HELLO, AREA L-7,
CAN I HELP YOU?
IT'S ETEMON!
YES, SIR!
HEY, LITTLE BUNNY,
YOU'LL BE HAVING
SOME GUESTS SOON.
YOU BETTER GET READY
TO WELCOME THEM.
WELCOME THEM?
SO, DO YOU MEAN--
BINGO, BUNNY!
AS YOU WISH, SIR!
Izzy: AMAZING! IT LOOKS
LIKE THE ROMAN COLISEUM.
Tentomon: WHAT'S
THE ROMAN COLISEUM?
WELL, TENTOMON,
IT'S AN ANCIENT ARENA.
Mimi: BUT THE ANCIENT ONE
DIDN'T HAVE BIG SCREENS!
Sora: OR SOCCER GOALS!
OK, LET'S SPLIT UP
AND LOOK FOR THE CREST!
OHHH!
WHAT'S WRONG?
I CAN'T MOVE ANYMORE.
LEMME REST
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
COME ON, GET UP!
YOU CAN DO IT!
I CAN'T.
GIVE HIM
A REST,
TAI.
HMM?
THE ONLY CLUE
WE HAVE IS MY TAG,
SO GOMAMON AND I WILL
SEARCH FOR THE CREST.
YOU GUYS RELAX.
LATER!
Tai: WAIT,
I'LL GO WITH YOU!
A SOCCER BALL!
HEY, ANYBODY
UP FOR A GAME?
All: YEAH! SOUNDS FUN!
THAT'S
A GREAT IDEA!
THE HUMAN TEAM
WILL PLAY AGAINST
THE DIGIMON TEAM.
WHAT ON EARTH
IS SOCCER?
IT'S EASY.
USE YOUR FEET TO GET
THIS BALL IN THE GOAL.
YOU CAN ALSO USE
YOUR CHEST OR YOUR HEAD.
HERE I GO!
AAAH!
THAT'S REALLY
USING YOUR HEAD!
OH, AND I FORGOT
TO TELL YOU,
YOU CAN'T USE
YOUR HANDS.
UNLESS YOU'RE
THE GOALKEEPER,
THEN YOU CAN
USE YOUR HANDS!
YEAH, YOU SHOULD
BE THE GOALIE FOR
YOUR TEAM, PALMON.
HERE!
WAAHH!
UGH!
HUH?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE PLAYING SOCCER
AT A TIME LIKE THIS!
USE YOUR HEADS
FOR SOMETHING OTHER THAN
HITTING THE BALL!
THE SOONER JOE FINDS
THE CREST, THE SOONER
WE CAN LEAVE!
YOUR TAG IS
REACTING AGAIN!
YEAH, THE CREST
MUST BE HERE SOMEWHERE.
HUH?
[ETEMON LAUGHING]
WHO'S THE KING?
AAH! HE'S HERE!
ETEMON'S HERE!
[ETEMON LAUGHS]
HEY, WAIT FOR ME!
AAHHH!
AGUMON!
ALL: HUH?
WE'RE TRAPPED!
Etemon: GOAAAL!
I SURE DID IT!
I SCORED A GOAL!
THE WHOLE THING
WAS A TRAP!
DOES HE REALLY THINK
HE CAN TRAP US
WITH A SIMPLE NET?
YEOOOOW!
All: OH!
Etemon:
NOW LISTEN UP.
IF YOU DO THAT,
YOU MIGHT GET HURT.
THERE'S ELECTRICITY
RUNNING THROUGH THAT NET.
IT'S A SHOCKER,
I KNOW.
I REALLY WANTED
TO BE THERE IN PERSON
TO DO THIS MYSELF,
BUT I'M WAY TOO BUSY.
YOU KNOW HOW US
ROCK AND ROLL LEGENDS ARE.
BUT DON'T WORRY,
THE ACT SUBSTITUTING
FOR ME IS A VERY RARE TREAT.
LET'S SEE IF YOU CAN
FIGURE OUT WHO OUR
SPECIAL GUEST STAR IS.
WELL?
HOW WOULD WE KNOW
WHO IT IS?
I'M SURE
YOU'LL BE SURPRISED!
HERE HE COMES!
IT'S A DIFFERENT
GREYMON!
RRRRRRAAAARGGH!
I KNEW YOU'D
BE SURPRISED.
I'M SO EVIL!
LET'S GET STARTED!
IT'S TIME TO GO.
OK, HERE'S THE SHOW.
MMMMMAAAAAGH!
IT'S TIME TO DIGIVOLVE!
AGUMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
GREYMON!
YOU CAN DO IT,
DON'T LOSE TO
THAT PHONEY-BALONEY!
GREYMON, YOU'VE
GOT TO DIGIVOLVE!
Izzy: THIS
DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
Tentomon: WE'RE DONE FOR
IF HE CAN'T DIGIVOLVE AGAIN!
[EVIL LAUGHTER]
Evil Greymon: MMUHAHAHA!
DIGIVOLVE, GREYMON!
YOU'VE GOT TO!
WHAT'S HE WAITING FOR?
WHY WON'T HE DIGIVOLVE
TO THE NEXT LEVEL?
IT'S NOT WORKING, TAI.
THE CREST ISN'T
REACTING AT ALL.
MAYBE YOU GAVE HIM
TOO MUCH TO EAT.
MAYBE HE CAN'T
DIGIVOLVE.
OF COURSE
HE CAN.
COME ON, GREYMON,
YOU CAN DO IT.
BELIEVE IN YOUR POWER
AND YOU CAN DIGIVOLVE.
WAY TO GO, GREYMON!
NOVA BLAST!
[BURP]
HE CERTAINLY DOESN'T
HAVE ANY DIGIMANNERS.
AT LEAST SAY EXCUSE ME.
AM I IMAGINING IT,
OR IS HE MOVING
A LOT SLOWER
THAN USUAL?
HE CONSUMED
WAY TOO MUCH,
SO HIS REFLEXES
ARE SLUGGISH.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
IZZY.
OW! NOT AGAIN.
GET UP AND FIGHT!
IT'S LOOKING LIKE THIS
IS GONNA BE OVER
SOONER THAN I THOUGHT.
HA HA HA!
HA HA HA! HUH?
Etemon: YOU SILLY RABBIT,
STOP CARRYING ON
LIKE A TRAINED SEAL.
GET THE FIREWORKS READY
SO I CAN CELEBRATE MY VICTORY.
YES, SIR.
WE REALLY NEED HELP.
MARCHING FISHES!
YAP! WAAAH!
Joe: WHERE DID
THOSE FISH COME FROM?
HOW COULD THEY JUST COME
OUT OF THERE LIKE THAT?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT
IF IT'S NOT BROKEN,
DON'T FIX IT.
IT'S REALLY
ELEMENTARY, JOE.
THERE'S PROBABLY JUST
A DIMENSIONAL VORTEX RIFT
IN THE WATER.
DITTO.
OH.
THANK YOU, FISH!
NOW, WHAT ARE WE GOING
TO DO TO GET OUT OF HERE?
WE SHOULD DIG A HOLE
AND TUNNEL OUR WAY OUT.
GOOD IDEA.
Izzy: THERE'S
A BLACK CABLE HERE, TOO.
Tentomon: THIS ROCK
IS IN THE WAY.
MY TAG...IT'S...IT'S
REACTING AGAIN.
WHAT IF THIS ROCK
IS THE CREST WE'VE
BEEN LOOKING FOR?
IF THIS REALLY IS
THE CREST THAT GOES WITH
MY TAG, THEN MAYBE...
All: WAAA!
All: AAAH!
IT IS MY CREST! YES!
LOOK, A TUNNEL.
WE CAN GET OUT
THROUGH HERE.
Etemon: HOW DO
YOU LIKE THAT?
NOT ONLY DID THOSE
LITTLE DARLINGS ESCAPE,
BUT THEY FOUND
ANOTHER CREST TOO.
THIS IS UNFORGIVABLE!
GREYMON, YOU COULD WIN
IF YOU'D ONLY DIGIVOLVE.
GREYMON!
TAI, DON'T.
DON'T STOP ME.
THIS IS MY CHANCE
TO MAKE HIM
DIGIVOLVE
TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
PLEASE MIND YOUR
OWN BUSINESS, SORA.
BUT, TAI,
WITHOUT A REACTION
FROM THE CREST,
THERE'S NO WAY FOR
HIM TO DIGIVOLVE.
I CAN MAKE HIM DO IT.
WATCH!
WHAT DO YOU THINK
HE'S GONNA DO?
THE OTHER CONDITION
FOR DIGIVOLVING
IS THEIR PARTNER
MUST BE IN DANGER.
Sora: HE WOULDN'T!
HURRY UP AND
FINISH HIM OFF!
USE YOUR NOVA BLAST!
HA HA HA!
Tai: STOP!
I'M NOT AFRAID OF
A BIG FAKE LIKE YOU.
OK, FIRE BREATH,
COME AND GET ME!
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
A DOPE WHO THINKS
HE'S A SUPERSTAR?
WELL, YOU GOT IT. NOW START
SINGING YOUR FINAL NUMBER.
AAH!
BIYOMON, YOU'VE
GOT TO HELP TAI.
YOU GO, TOO,
GABUMON.
GOT IT.
BIYOMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
BIRDRAMON!
GABUMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
GARURUMON!
Tai: GREYMON,
I BELIEVE IN YOU!
YOU CAN DO IT, GREYMON!
DIGIVOLVE!
OH!
WHAT IN THE WORLD?
WHAT DO YOU
THINK THAT IS?
OH, MY! IS THAT
WHAT I THINK IT IS?
WHAT DO YOU
CALL THAT THING?
Tentomon: SKULL GREYMON.
THE SIGHT OF HIM MAKES
OTHER DIGIMON TREMBLE.
HE IS A FULLY
DIGIVOLVED DIGIMON
WHOSE EXPLOSIVE POWER
CAUSES HIM TO CONSTANTLY
SEARCH FOR BATTLE.
THIS COULD
BE VERY BAD.
THERE'S BEEN
SOME MISTAKE,
AND HE'S DIGIVOLVED
INTO A HORRIBLE MONSTER.
THIS IS GREYMON'S
DIGIVOLVED FORM?
WHOA!
LISTEN TO ME,
SKULL GREYMON.
IF YOU'RE REALLY
THE DIGIVOLVED
FORM OF GREYMON,
THEN YOU CAN'T
HURT ME!
Matt: TAI,
GET OUT OF THERE!
LEAVE IT TO ME!
TENTOMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
KABUTERIMON!
OH, NO!
AAH!
OH, NO! MY POOR NETWORK.
THEY'RE DESTROYING
EVERYTHING
THAT I WORKED
SO HARD TO CREATE. AAH!
All: AAH!
METEOR WING!
HOWLING BLASTER!
ELECTRO SHOCKER!
Izzy: I WONDER
WHAT HAPPENED.
Tentomon:
HIS ENERGY RAN OUT.
T.K.: HE'S KOROMON AGAIN!
WHOA!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WELL, YES...BUT...
I'VE DONE SOME TERRIBLE,
HORRIBLE THINGS.
I SAVAGELY ATTACKED
3 OF MY FELLOW DIGIMONS.
IT WASN'T
YOUR FAULT.
SHE'S RIGHT.
WE COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND.
I'M REALLY SORRY
I DIDN'T LIVE UP
TO YOUR EXPECTATIONS
OF ME, TAI.
Matt: IT'S NOT
YOUR FAULT.
I KNOW WHO'S
TO BLAME.
I KNOW, IT'S
ALL MY FAULT.
I'M REALLY,
REALLY SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO PUT
IT ALL ON YOU, TAI.
IT'S OK.
IT'S MY FAULT.
RIGHT, SORA?
YEAH, I MEAN--
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
I WAS DOING,
BUT I KEPT PUSHING
PEOPLE AROUND
ANYWAY.
I FELT LIKE BECAUSE
I HAD THE CREST,
I HAD TO BE
IN CHARGE AND
FIGHT ON MY OWN
WITHOUT ANY HELP
FROM THE REST
OF YOU.
I'M SORRY, EVERYBODY.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME
YOU WERE FINALLY ABLE TO
DIGIVOLVE
BUT IT WAS A HUGE MISTAKE
I WONDER IF OUR DIGIMON WILL
EVER
BE ABLE TO DIGIVOLVE THE RIGHT
WAY.
ONE THING'S FOR SURE, I LEARNED
MY LESSSON.