Izzy: I HAD MY HANDS FULL
LOOKING FOR THAT EIGHTH CHILD
AND TRYING TO HIDE TENTOMON
FROM MY PARENTS.
THERE WAS A STRANGE
DIGIVICE SIGNAL
MOVING ALL OVER TOWN.
IT CONFUSED EVERYBODY,
INCLUDING DEMIDEVIMON.
MEANWHILE, KABUTERIMON
REALLY GOT A NOSE-FULL
WHEN HE WENT UP
AGAINST RAREMON,
A VERY ODOROUS DIGIMON
WITH A BODY STRUCTURE
UNLIKE ANY
I'VE EVER SEEN BEFORE,
BUT ULTIMATELY HE WAS NO MATCH
FOR KABUTERIMON.
MOST CURIOUS.
WITH ALL THIS EXCITEMENT,
YOU'D THINK WE WERE BACK
IN THE DIGIWORLD.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Myotismon: AH, DARKNESS --
THE PERFECT CLOAK
FOR MY EVIL.
IDEAL CONDITIONS
FOR PRODUCING FEAR.
HUMAN BLOOD ALWAYS TASTES BETTER
WITH A DASH OF FEAR IN IT.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT IS THAT, A CARRIAGE?
AAH!
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ MOANS ]
I HATE THIS FOG!
MASTER, WHERE ARE YOU?
I'M GETTING MILDEW
ON MY WINGS.
AHA!
FINALLY!
SHEESH! HE COULDN'T TAKE A CAB
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE?
[ WOMAN MOANS ]
AT LAST.
I WAS STARTING TO WORRY.
CALM DOWN.
I WENT OUT TO HAVE
A BITE TO EAT
AND TO GET FAMILIAR
WITH THE CITY.
ALWAYS DIFFICULT
TO GET A GOOD MEAL
WHEN AWAY FROM HOME.
YEAH, RIGHT. SO WHAT
DO WE DO NEXT, BOSS?
WE ARE CONTINUING THE SEARCH
FOR THE EIGHTH CHILD.
THE DETAILS ARE
OF NO CONCERN TO YOU.
WELL, AS I ALWAYS SAY,
UH, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
Tai: AW, COME ON.
WHERE DID I PUT
THAT THING?
JUNK.
STUFF.
MORE JUNK. MORE STUFF.
MAN, I WAS A MESSY KID.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW UNORGANIZED I WAS.
WHOA! OH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LOOKING FOR
MY OLD PHONE BOOK.
IT'LL HAVE
EXACTLY WHAT I NEED.
I'M HELPING.
HOW COME?
Man: NOW TODAY'S TOP STORY --
THE MONSTERS
THAT ARE PLAGUING THE CITY.
STILL NO OFFICIAL COMMENT
ON WHERE THE CREATURES ARE FROM
OR WHAT THEY MIGHT BE AFTER.
WE WILL KEEP YOU UPDATED
THROUGHOUT THE DAY.
MEANWHILE, IN OTHER NEWS,
HEALTH OFFICIALS REPORT
YOUNG WOMEN ALL OVER THE CITY
ARE BEING HOSPITALIZED
FOR ANEMIA...
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
JUST A MOMENT!
BUT DOCTORS
ARE VOICING CONCERN
THAT SO MANY SEEMINGLY
HEALTHY YOUNG WOMEN
ARE BEING STRUCK DOWN
SO SUDDENLY.
TAI, IT'S YOUR FRIEND IZZY.
Tai: COMING!
[ HUMMING ]
OOP!
[ GIGGLES ]
HEY.
HEY, READY TO GO?
AGUMON, YOU DIGEVOLVED.
YOU BET I DID.
ALL I NEEDED
WAS A GOOD MEAL.
PSST. IT'S ME.
TENTOMON.
NICE DISGUISE, DUDE.
THANKS, TAI.
I PUT IT TOGETHER MYSELF.
WAIT TILL MIMI SEES YOU.
I NEED ONE, TOO.
YEAH. ANY IDEAS?
MM-HMM.
[ CHATTERING ]
Tai: YEAH, REAL INCONSPICUOUS.
SO, TAI, DID YOU FIND
YOUR ADDRESS BOOK FROM SCHOOL?
OH, UH, WELL,
SORA WAS IN MY CLASS,
SO I THOUGHT
WE'D JUST USE HERS.
UH-HUH.
COULDN'T FIND IT, HUH?
Tai: ALL RIGHT,
LISTEN UP, EVERYBODY.
I CALLED YOU ALL HERE TODAY
BECAUSE, WELL, UH,
THERE WAS NOTHING GOOD ON TV.
Matt: VERY FUNNY, TAI.
WHERE ARE THE OTHERS?
WAIT!
DON'T START WITHOUT ME.
OH, GOOD MORNING.
Tentomon: OKAY,
SO WHERE'S MIMI?
Izzy: PROBABLY OUT
BUYING CLOTHES.
GET OUT AND WALK.
YOU'RE TOO HEAVY TO PUSH.
HOW'S THAT GOING TO LOOK?
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE A BABY.
YOU JUST GREW UP.
NOW GET OUT.
HEY, DID YOU GUYS SEE IT?
IT WAS ALL OVER THE NEWS
ON TV THIS MORNING.
MORE AND MORE OF MYOTISMON'S
DIGIBOZOS ARE POPPING UP.
AND THEY'RE VERY REAL.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LAST TIME WE CAME BACK,
THERE WERE DIGIMON ALL OVER,
BUT ONLY KARI AND I
COULD SEE THEM.
EVERYBODY ELSE
WALKED RIGHT BY THEM
AS IF THEY WEREN'T
EVEN THERE.
NOW EVEN NORMAL PEOPLE
SEE THEM,
AND THEY'RE ON THE NEWS.
IT'S LIKE THEY'RE REALLY HERE
THIS TIME.
MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE THIS TIME
THEY CAME THROUGH THE GATE
THAT MYOTISMON MADE.
IF THEY CAN BE SEEN,
THEN THEY'RE PHYSICALLY HERE.
AND IF THEY'RE HERE PHYSICALLY,
THEY CAN DO
A WHOLE LOT OF DAMAGE.
YEAH? LIKE WHAT?
Matt: DO I REALLY NEED
TO REMIND YOU
WHAT THOSE EVIL DIGIMON
ARE CAPABLE OF?
CREEPY.
COMPLETE SYSTEMS FAILURE.
SO WHAT ARE WE SITTING
AROUND HERE FOR?
WE BETTER FIND THAT EIGHTH KID
TO STOP THESE GUYS.
SAVE THE DIGIWORLD,
AND WE'LL SAVE OUR OWN.
UH-HUH.
Matt: WHAT'S THE PLAN?
Izzy: WELL, I THOUGHT --
STOP!
DON'T START UNTIL I GET THERE!
I LOVE IZZY'S THEORIES!
ALL RIGHT. WE WON'T
START WITHOUT YOU.
Izzy: WE'VE ALREADY CONCLUDED
THAT WHEN THE DIGIMON
ATTACKED FOUR YEARS AGO,
ALL OF US, INCLUDING
THE EIGHTH CHILD, WERE THERE.
IT IS SAFE TO ASSUME
THAT EACH OF US WERE GIVEN
DIGIVICES FOR A REASON.
LAST NIGHT I PICKED UP
AN UNIDENTIFIED
DIGIVICE READING.
I THINK IT WAS
THE EIGHTH CHILD.
OBVIOUSLY, I LOST THE SIGNAL,
BUT IT'S CLEAR THE EIGHTH CHILD
IS IN THIS VICINITY.
THAT'S WHY THE MONSTERS
ARE HERE, TOO.
MONSTERS! WORSE THAN SNAKES!
AND THIS IS SUPPOSED
TO HELP US? I'M LOST.
MY CONCLUSION
IS THAT THE EIGHTH CHILD
IS SOMEWHERE IN ONE
OF THESE ADDRESS BOOKS.
WE HAVE TO MAKE CALLS
AND PATROL THE CITY
FOR MONSTER ATTACKS.
I COULD DO SOME CALLING,
LONG AS MY FOLKS
DON'T FIND OUT,
BUT I GOT TO DO
SOME SERIOUS STUDYING,
SO I WON'T BE ABLE
TO SEARCH WITH YOU.
WHAT? JOE, IT'S SUMMER.
I'M GETTING AN EARLY START.
THIS YEAR I'M REALLY
GOING TO BE PREPARED.
HERE THEN. IF YOU'RE
NOT COMING WITH US,
THEN YOU MIGHT AS WELL
DO MY CALLING FOR ME.
JOE, WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
THE FATE OF THE WORLD.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO CHICKEN OUT,
YOU CAN CALL ALL THE NAMES
IN MY BOOK, TOO!
IT MIGHT MAKE MORE SENSE
HAVING ONE PERSON
CONCENTRATE ON CALLING
RATHER THAN SPLIT IT UP.
HE HAS A POINT THERE.
GOOD LUCK.
WAIT A MINUTE.
NO, TAI!
NOT YOURS, TOO! PLEASE!
I'M NOT THAT KIND OF GUY.
DON'T WORRY.
YOU'VE GOT ENOUGH
ON YOUR PLATE.
OH, MAN, TAI,
YOU'RE A TOTALLY GREAT GUY.
THANKS.
AH, WELL, YOU KNOW.
MR. GENEROUS.
I BET HE COULDN'T FIND
HIS ADDRESS BOOK.
WELL,
HOW'D YOU EVER GUESS?
LOOK AT ALL THAT DAMAGE
FROM LAST NIGHT'S BATTLE.
THERE WILL BE A LOT MORE
IF THIS GOES ON.
WE'VE GO TO FIND
THAT EIGHTH CHILD.
Matt: WE WILL.
WE'RE NOT CALLED
THE DIGIDESTINED FOR NOTHING.
MASTER,
ARE WE ALMOST THERE YET?
'CAUSE ALL THIS WATER
IS MAKING ME QUEASY.
Demidevimon:
THOSE DIGIDESTINED BRATS
ARE PROBABLY MILES AWAY
BY NOW.
Man: HEY, LOOK.
THAT FOG'S
COMING IN AGAIN.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
AT THE SAME TIME,
WE'RE HAVING THE HOTTEST
WEATHER ON RECORD.
I HEARD SOMEBODY SAW
SNOW FALLING LAST NIGHT.
THE OZONE LAYER MUST BE
WORSE THAN WE THOUGHT.
Gatomon: WELCOME, O GREAT ONE.
ALL IS READY.
PERFECT, GATOMON.
AS ALWAYS,
YOU HAVE DONE EXCELLENT WORK.
HEY, WHISKERS,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
I DON'T THINK.
I KNOW WHY I'M HERE.
I'M FINDING
THE EIGHTH CHILD.
THAT'S MY JOB, FURBALL!
I'M IN CHARGE HERE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
LISTEN UP,
PUSS-IN-BOOTS,
QUIT SUCKING UP
TO THE MASTER.
"I'M THE MASTER'S
CUTE LITTLE PET."
GAG ME WITH A FURBALL!
IT'S HARD
TO FEEL THREATENED
BY A BOWLING BALL
WITH FEATHERS.
JUST KEEP OUT OF MY WAY.
I'M FINDING THAT KID,
NOT YOU, GOT IT?
TAKE A CATNAP,
KITTY LITTER!
HA HA!
[ Thinking ]
THAT FLAPPY-WINGED JOKER
COULDN'T FIND WATER
IF HE FELL OUT OF A BOAT.
Tai: WE'LL SPLIT UP
INTO PAIRS SO WE CAN COVER MORE
OF THE CITY.
Izzy: LET'S GO.
GOOD LUCK, EVERYBODY.
I SEE FOOD.
AGUMON, KEEP YOUR MIND
ON OUR MISSION, OKAY?
ANYTHING?
CAN'T CATCH ME! HA HA!
COME ON!
YEAH, YOU GOT IT!
[ LAUGHING ]
NO, THERE'S NOTHING YET.
WELL, IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE HE'S DOWN HERE.
THAT WOULD'VE BEEN
TOO EASY, ANYWAY.
YEAH, RIGHT.
HI, I KNOW
THIS IS KIND OF STRANGE,
BUT I WAS IN SECOND GRADE
WITH YOU...
HEY, STOP PUSHING!
I AM NOT PUSHING YOU!
YOU'RE KICKING ME!
YOU CROSSED THE LINE
ON TO MY SIDE, YOU CHEATER!
I AM NOT A CHEATER!
YOU'RE A LIAR!
KNOCK IT OFF.
SOMEONE'S GOING TO GET HURT.
I KNOW HOW THEY FEEL.
WALKING AROUND
IN THIS HEAT
IS ENOUGH TO MAKE
ANYBODY CRANKY.
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS, SORA?
A BIG FAT DRAG.
[ CHATTERING ]
WHAT SILLY CREATURES.
PEA-BRAINED DOLTS.
LAUGH IT UP.
WHEN MYOTISMON IS THROUGH,
YOU WON'T BE LAUGHING.
MIKO, COME BACK HERE!
WHERE DID YOU GO?
MIKO!
WHAT A FUNNY LOOKING KITTY.
HI, THERE.
ARE YOU A FRIEND OF AGUMON?
HUH?
ARE YOU ONE OF THEM?
[ MEOWS ]
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
WAIT! DON'T GO!
[ GROANS ]
Gatomon: [ Thinking ]
SO, SHE KNOWS ABOUT AGUMON.
HMM. IS IT POSSIBLE
THIS LITTLE SQUIRT
IS THE EIGHTH CHILD?
HEY, I KNOW YOU'RE THERE.
[ SCREECHES ]
YOU CAN COME IN
IF YOU WANT TO.
MOM'S NOT HOME.
Woman: WEATHER EXPERTS CAN'T
EXPLAIN THE UNSEASONABLE FOG.
THEY HAVE NO EXPLANATION
FOR ANY OF THE BIZARRE WEATHER
WE'VE BEEN HAVING,
INCLUDING THIS HEAT WAVE.
I'M NOT MEANT
FOR THIS KIND OF WORK.
IF I EVER HAVE A BABY,
I'M GOING TO HIRE SOMEBODY
TO PUSH HER AROUND.
HOLD ON. HOW ABOUT
A BREAK, OKAY?
AGAIN?
WELL, MAKE IT QUICK.
AHH.
LAST NIGHT I GOT TO SLEEP
IN A SOFT BED
WITH THE A.C. CRANKED UP,
WATCHING MY OWN TV.
DINNER WAS
REALLY SOMETHING, TOO.
WASN'T IT GREAT?
MY MOM KNOWS ALL THE BEST
TAKE-OUT PLACES.
SHE NEVER HAS TO COOK.
SORA'S MOM MADE OUR DINNER,
AND IT WAS TERRIFIC,
ALL EXCEPT FOR THIS
KIND OF GREEN MUSHY STUFF.
WHAT'S IT CALLED?
WHAT? SPINACH.
NOW, LET'S SEE.
WHERE WAS I?
HMM.
LOOK AT THAT?
SHE'S NOT EVEN TIRED.
YOU'RE DIFFERENT.
YOU LIKE TO
TAKE THINGS EASY.
FINDING THIS KID'S HARDER
THAN FINDING A GOOD SALE.
[ GASPS ]
HEY, SORA, IF WE REALLY
WANT TO FIND THIS KID,
WE SHOULD GO WHERE
LOTS OF PEOPLE GATHER.
ANY PLACE IN PARTICULAR?
YEP, RIGHT THERE.
[ GIGGLES ]
BESIDES, WE CAN SEE
THE WHOLE CITY
FROM UP THERE,
REALLY GET THE LAY
OF THE LAND, YOU KNOW?
Woman: THIS IS GREAT.
I'VE NEVER BEEN HERE BEFORE.
Boy: WOW!
LOOK HOW HIGH IT GOES!
Man: I CAN SEE
THE WHOLE CITY.
Man #2: YES.
IT'S MARVELOUS, ISN'T IT?
AHH. THERE.
ISN'T THAT BETTER?
NICE AND COOL.
I KNEW THIS PLACE
WOULD HAVE A.C.
FEELS GREAT!
SHOULD HAVE GUESSED
YOU HAD AN ULTERIOR MOTIVE.
ISN'T YOUR HOUSE
OVER THERE?
YEAH.
IT SURE IS STRANGE
BEING BACK
IN OUR OWN WORLD AGAIN.
DOES IT FEEL LIKE
IT'S GETTING WARMER?
YEAH, IT DOES.
LET'S MOVE OVER CLOSER
TO THE BLOWERS.
THERE. THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
WONDERFUL.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE AIR?
Man: WHAT IS THAT?
DID IT JUST TURN OFF?
MAYBE THIS HEAT
GOT TO BE TOO MUCH FOR IT.
LOOK AT THAT WEIRDO WEARING
A COAT IN THIS HEAT --
SUCH AN UGLY ONE, TOO.
HEY, MIMI, BE QUIET.
HE'LL HEAR YOU.
WHAT'S HE GOING TO DO?
Sora: SEE? HE HEARD YOU.
I TOLD YOU.
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GROWLS ]
UH-OH!
[ ROARS ]
Mimi: WELL, I GUESS
THAT EXPLAINS THE COAT.
DID IT JUST GET HOTTER
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
I DIDN'T NOTICE.
LOOK UP AT THE TOWER.
IT'S ALMOST
LIKE IT'S BENDING.
IMPOSSIBLE!
WAIT A MINUTE.
HUH? OH, NO!
WE GOT TROUBLE!
[ SCREECHING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
METEOR WING!
GET READY
FOR MY NEEDLE SPRAY!
GRR!
OOH!
TOGEMON!
AAH!
[ LAUGHING ]
HUH?
EXPLAIN THIS TO US, AGUMON.
JUST WHO IS THIS GUY?
HE'S SKULLMERAMON.
HIS ELEMENT IS FIRE.
HE'S TOUGH,
AND HE CAN SURE DISH IT OUT.
GRR! METAL FIREBALL!
Tai: THE TOWER'S GOING TO
FALL ON THE CITY.
GRAB IT, KABUTERIMON!
HURRY!
DON'T YOU KNOW
NOT TO PLAY WITH FIRE?
ARE YOU READY?
YEAH!
AGUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GREYMON!
[ ROARS ]
OOH!
NOVA BLAST!
[ LAUGHING ]
[ GROWLING ]
Tai: GREAT.
NOW WE'VE REALLY
MADE HIM MAD.
HE SWALLOWED THAT BLAST
LIKE A HOT FUDGE SUNDAE.
ALL IT DID
WAS MAKE HIM STRONGER.
UNLESS GREYMON DIGEVOLVES AGAIN,
HE'S TOAST!
GREYMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
METAL GREYMON!
[ ROARS ]
LIGHT-SPEED JABBING!
WATCH OUT!
THIS GUY IS SCARY!
OH! HOT! WHOO-HOO!
METAL FIREBALL!
[ SHRIEKS ]
HEY, UP HERE,
BUCKET OF BOLTS.
HUH?
MEGA-CLAW!
I'VE GOT YOU!
[ GRUNTING ]
METAL FIREBALL!
GRR! WHO'S GOT WHO NOW?
HUH?
[ SCREAMING ]
GIGA-BLASTER!
Man: WHILE THE CLASH OF THE MONSTERS
CAUSED DAMAGE TO THE TOWER...
Gatomon: [ Thinking ]
SHE ISN'T SO BAD,
FOR A HUMAN.
BETTER COMPANY
THAN SOME DIGIMON.
BUT FEAR IS IN THE AIR,
AND THERE'S A GENERAL FEELING
OF PUBLIC UNREST.
NOW BACK
TO OUR REGULAR PROGRAMMING.
STILL, ORDERS ARE ORDERS,
AND I'M NOT
GOING TO BE THE ONE
WHO LETS THE EIGHTH CHILD
GET AWAY.
HUH?
COME HERE.
UH, WHOA!
ARE YOU GOING ALREADY?
BUT YOU'LL COME BACK
AGAIN, RIGHT?
HER SWEETNESS
MAKES ME LOSE MY EDGE,
BUT NEXT TIME
I'LL BE READY FOR HER.
Man: WHILE NO ONE KNOWS
WHERE THESE MONSTERS ARE FROM
OR WHY THEY'RE HERE,
IT'S CLEAR THE EARTH
IS AT SOME SORT OF CROSSROADS.
DOWN WHICH ROAD
DOES OUR DESTINY AWAIT?