WE GOT INTO THIS AMAZING BATTLE
AGAINST VENOMMYOTISMON
GREYMON AND GARURUMON DIGIVOLVED
TO MEGA FOR THE FIRST TIME
BUT THAT
COULDN'T STOP HIM.
FINALLY, WE COMBINED
ALL OUR POWERS,
AND THAT TOTALLY BLASTED
VENOMMYOTISMON INTO DIGIDUST.
AFTERWARDS, THE DIGITAL WORLD
APPEARED IN THE SKY.
IZZY FIGURED THAT WHILE
WE'VE BEEN ON EARTH,
THINGS HAVE GOTTEN WORSE
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
WE'RE GOING BACK
TO FIX THE PROBLEMS.
IT WAS A BUMMER TO LEAVE
OUR PARENTS SO SOON,
BUT SAVING TWO WORLDS
IS KIND OF IMPORTANT.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HA HA HA!
THOSE BIT PLAYERS
ARE FROZEN WITH STAGE FRIGHT,
HOPELESSLY WAITING
FOR THE MOMENT THEY'LL BE SAVED.
THERE'S AN UNSEEN TWIST
IN THE PLOT.
I SAY WE CUT
TO THE PUNCH LINE
AND GO STRAIGHT
FOR THE ACTION.
OH, PLEASE,
THAT WOULD BE BORING.
I WANT TO PLAY THIS DRAMA
TO THE HILT!
LET'S PULL OUT
ALL THE STOPS
AND GIVE THEM
WHAT THEY PAID FOR.
I'M IN COMPLETE AGREEMENT.
A QUICK VICTORY
WOULD BE A LETDOWN.
THE DIGIDESTINED WILL BE
ON SPIRAL MOUNTAIN SOON.
WE MUST REHEARSE
BEFORE THEY GET HERE.
IT WILL BE
THEIR FINAL PERFORMANCE!
METALSEADRAMON,
PUPPETMON,
AND MACHINEDRAMON,
I PRESENT TO YOU
THE DOWNFALL
OF THE DIGIDESTINED!
All: AAH!
OH...WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE BACK.
Mimi: BACK WHERE,
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD?
THAT'S AFFIRMATIVE.
T.K.: IT'S DARK!
Joe: YEAH,
IT'S KIND OF WEIRD.
HUH?
HEY, LOOK UP THERE!
[ ALL GASP ]
TALK ABOUT WEIRD!
Joe: COULD THAT BE EARTH?
IT'S MERELY SPECULATION,
BUT IT SEEMS TO BE
A REASONABLE FACSIMILE.
WE SEE EARTH FROM HERE
LIKE WE SAW THE DIGITAL WORLD
FROM EARTH.
HUH?
GOMAMON --
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU?
JOE, I'VE BEEN SNOOZING
OVER HERE.
HUH? OH, WE'LL JUST SAVE
THE WORLD WITHOUT YOU, THEN.
AAH!
JOE!
WHOA! I DIDN'T NEED THIS.
KOROMON DIGEVOLVE TO AGUMON.
TSUNOMON DIGEVOLVE TO GABUMON.
MOGIMON DIGEVOLVE TO TENTOMON.
TOGEMON DIGEVOLVE TO PATAMON.
YOKOMON DIGEVOLVE TO BIYOMON.
HOLD ON!
HUH?
COME OUT!
YOU'RE AMONG FRIENDS.
WE WON'T HURT YOU.
DON'T BE AFRAID.
OH, MY GOODNESS,
IT'S CHUMON.
HE LOOKS TERRIBLE.
WHAT HE NEEDS
IS A COMPLETE MAKEOVER.
MIMI?
HA HA HA!
TSUKOMON AND CHUMON
USED TO BE INSEPARABLE.
I'M SO GLAD YOU
CAME BACK TO SAVE US.
OH.
Joe: WOULD SOMEBODY
MIND HELPING ME?
WHOOPS, I FORGOT
ALL ABOUT YOU. UH-OH.
I'M HANGING HERE BY MY ELBOWS,
AND YOU'RE OFF IN LA-LA LAND!
I WONDER WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO HAVE ELBOWS.
JOE! FIGURES.
HUH?
HEY, QUIT FOOLING AROUND!
AAH! JUST HELP ME,
WILL YOU?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
EVERYTHING'S GONE WACKO!
[ ALL GASP ]
ARE YOU TRYING TO GET
AHOLD OF GENNAI?
WELL, I'M NOT
PLAYING SOLITAIRE.
CHUMON'S A MESS.
I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM.
WELL, WHATEVER IT WAS,
IT WASN'T VERY PRETTY.
POOR THING.
AH, CHUMON!
MIMI! I WASN'T DREAMING.
IT'S REALLY YOU, AFTER ALL.
POOR THING!
WHY DON'T YOU TELL MIMI
ALL ABOUT IT?
OH.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR FRIEND TSUKOMON?
I-I...I'M AFRAID I LOST HIM.
Chumon: AFTER YOU GUYS
LEFT FIRE ISLAND,
TSUKOMON AND I WENT ON
WITH LIFE AS USUAL.
YOU KNOW, EATING, EATING,
AND MORE EATING
WHEN SUDDENLY...
AAH!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
WHOA! AAH!
TSUKOMON!
AAH!
I NEVER SAW HIM AGAIN.
A POWERFUL EVIL FORCE
TOOK OVER THE LAND,
CAUSING ALL KINDS
OF BAD THINGS TO HAPPEN.
THEN IT REBUILT
THE DIGITAL WORLD
SO IT WOULD BE EASIER
TO CONQUER.
I'VE BEEN HIDING
EVER SINCE.
Tai: YOU MEAN THE DIGITAL WORLD
IS COMPLETELY CHANGED
FROM WHAT IT WAS?
HOW'S IT DIFFERENT?
EVERYTHING'S
BEEN DISCOMBOBULATED
AND TAKEN APART!
THE DIGITAL WORLD HAS BEEN
RELOCATED WAY UP THERE.
IT'S CALLED
SPIRAL MOUNTAIN.
[ ALL GASP ]
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
HERE OF THE OLD WORLD
EXCEPT SOME RUINS.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
IT'S ALL UP THERE? HUH.
COLOR ME CYNICAL,
BUT NOTHING SURPRISES ME
ABOUT THIS PLACE.
WHERE DID ALL
THE OTHER DIGIMON GO?
ARE THEY UP THERE, TOO?
WHERE'S LEOMON?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT FROM WHAT
I'VE BEEN TOLD,
THEY'LL DESTROY ANYTHING
THAT TRIES TO GET IN THEIR WAY.
WHO WILL?
WHO? THE DARK MASTERS.
WELL, THEY COULDN'T BE
TOO MUCH TOUGHER
THAN ANYBODY ELSE
WE'VE WRESTLED WITH BEFORE.
NO WAY!
THEY'LL BEAT THE PANTS
RIGHT OFF OF YOU.
WE GOT RID OF MYOTISMON,
SO WE COULD GET RID
OF THEM, TOO.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
AS LONG AS THE EIGHT OF US
ARE TOGETHER,
WE'LL KEEP THOSE BIG BULLIES
AWAY FROM YOU.
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU,
DIGIDESTINED.
[ KIDS SCREAM ]
OH, NO! IT'S METALSEADRAMON...
AND THIS GUY
IS ONE REAL HARD NOSE,
AND I MEAN HARD NOSE.
TAKE MY ADVICE,
THIS IS ONE TRAIN
THAT YOU WOULD RATHER MISS.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ SCREAMING ]
AAH!
[ GROWLS ]
OKAY, IF THAT'S THE WAY
YOU WANT IT,
WE CAN PLAY ROUGH, TOO.
[ GROWLS ]
LET'S GO, AGUMON.
GOT YOU.
AGUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GREYMON.
Gabumon: NOW IT'S OUR TURN.
GABUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GARURUMON.
TAILMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
BIRDRAMON.
TENTOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
KABUTERIMON.
GABUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
IKKAKUMON.
PALMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
TOGEMON.
PATAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
ANGEMON.
SALOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GATOMON.
[ GROWLS ]
NOVA BLAST!
[ METALSEADRAMON GROWLS ]
METEOR WING!
HOWLING BLASTER!
[ SCREAMING ]
ELECTROSHOCKER!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
HOW ABOUT
SOME NEEDLE SPRAY, HUH?
[ SCREAMING ]
Angemon: HAND OF FATE.
LIGHTENING PAW!
[ GROWLS ]
OOH!
ANGEMON!
YOU SHOULD KNOW YOUR POWERS
AREN'T STRONG ENOUGH.
HOW COME HE'S BEATING US
SO BADLY?
AH! IT'S BECAUSE
HE'S A MEGADIGIMON,
AND EVEN EIGHT CHAMPIONS
CAN'T OVERTAKE ONE MEGA.
HE'S STRONGER
THAN ALL OF US COMBINED.
THEN WE'RE LOST
WITHOUT MORE POWER.
EVER NOTICE WE'RE ALWAYS
AT THE WRONG PLACE
AT JUST THE WRONG TIME?
NOW IT'S TIME
TO TAKE ONE NASTY RIDE!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ MOANING ]
T.K., ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I THOUGHT I WAS BROKEN,
BUT I GUESS
I MUST BE OKAY.
[ LAUGHS ]
HUH?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WAIT. I'LL BE BACK.
AH! AAH!
ANGEMON!
AAH!
OH, NO! POOR PATOMON.
[ BOYS GASP ]
[ GROWLS ]
BE PREPARED
FOR ANOTHER MEGADIGIMON.
HE'S CALLED MACHINEDRAMON.
THIS METALLIC MUTANT
CAN BLOW OUT A DIGIMON
JUST LIKE A BIRTHDAY CANDLE.
GREYMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
METALGREYMON.
[ GROWLS ]
GARURUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
WEREGARURUMON.
[ HOWLS ]
KABUTERIMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
MEGAKABUTERIMON.
BIRDRAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GARUDAMON.
TOGEMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
LILLYMON.
IKKAKUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
ZUDOMON.
GATOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
ANGEWOMON.
COME ON. SHOW THEM
WHAT YOU'RE MADE OF.
HOPE THEY'RE MADE
OF SOMETHING STRONG ENOUGH.
MEGACANNON.
AAH!
OOH!
[ GROWLS ]
UHH!
ANGEWOMON!
AAH!
[ SCREAMING ]
WE STOPPED.
I CAN'T COMPLAIN.
IT'S SURE A LOT BETTER
THAN FALLING ON OUR HEADS.
HEY, CAN'T YOU TWO
TAKE A BREAK
FOR ONE MINUTE?
COME ON.
WE'RE ALL SUPPOSED TO BE
ON THE SAME SIDE.
I CAN'T CONTROL IT!
THAT'S RIGHT.
OUR BODIES ARE DOING THIS
ALL BY THEMSELVES.
ALL BY THEMSELVES, HUH? OH!
I'VE ALWAYS HATED
ANY FORM OF EXERCISE.
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
WE'VE BECOME
STRING PUPPETS,
AND SOMEONE'S
OPERATING US.
[ Laughs ] WELL, AREN'T WE
LITTLE SMARTY-PANTS.
WHO ARE YOU?
YOU WANT TO KNOW?
HOW ABOUT IF I HELP YOU
LOOK UP MY PROFILE
ON YOUR SPECIAL COMPUTER?
WATCH.
[ LAUGHS ]
HE'S ALSO A MEGADIGIMON.
PUPPETMON HAS
A CONTROLLING PERSONALITY
AND A ROTTEN TEMPER.
GET HIM MAD, AND HE'LL
BOP YOU WITH HIS HAMMER.
IF YOU HAVE
TO HIT SOMETHING,
BOP YOURSELF FOR HOW
YOU LOOK IN THAT HELMET.
I'M GOING TO HAVE
TO LET YOU GO FOR NOW.
I PROMISE TO DESTROY YOU --
NO STRINGS ATTACHED!
[ GROWLS ]
OH.
AAH!
MM.
AH.
OH!
OHH!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ MOANING AND GROANING ]
HUH?
WELL, HELLO THERE,
BOYS AND GIRLS, AND WELCOME.
TODAY I'M GOING TO TELL YOU
AN AMAZING STORY.
ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WERE EIGHT DIGIDESTINED.
THEY WENT
WITH THEIR DIGIMON COMPANIONS
TO TRY TO SAVE THE WORLD.
THE CHILDREN
AND THEIR DIGIMON DISCOVERED
THAT IN ORDER
FOR THEM TO DO IT,
THEY HAD TO CLIMB UP
TO THE TOP OF SPIRAL MOUNTAIN,
BUT TO THEIR DISMAY,
THE DARK MASTERS DEFEATED THEM.
HEY, CLOWNIE, NOBODY'S
LAUGHING AT YOUR STORY.
OH, DEAR! I'M SO SORRY.
DID I HAPPEN TO MENTION
THE STORY IS TRUE?
I WANTED TO GIVE YOU
A PREVIEW OF THE PLOT.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
FOOLS!
AAH! IT'S PIEDMON.
HE'S A MEGAPHANTOMDIGIMON
OF THE WORST KIND.
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT HE'S GOING
TO LOOK LIKE NEXT.
WELL, I THINK YOUR PLOT
NEEDS A FEW REWRITES.
AGUMON.
GABUMON,
YOU CAN DO IT.
AGUMON WARP-DIGEVOLVE TO...
WARGREYMON.
GABUMON WARP-DIGEVOLVE TO...
[ ROARS ]
METALGARURUMON.
YEAH!
LET THEM KNOW
WE MEAN BUSINESS,
WARGREYMON.
METALGARURUMON,
TEACH THAT JOKER A LESSON
HE'LL NEVER FORGET.
[ ROARS ]
NOVA FORCE!
HA!
ICE WOLF CLAW!
TRUMP SWORD!
AH!
[ ROARS ]
OH!
AAH! OH!
THIS IS BAD NEWS.
EVEN TWO MEGADIGIMON
COULDN'T PUT HIM DOWN.
THAT'S REALLY BAD NEWS.
NOT TO MENTION
HE'S A FASHION DISASTER.
YOUR TWO MEGAS
ARE NEWLY DIGEVOLVED.
HOW CAN YOU EXPECT THEM
TO COMPETE AGAINST
AN EXPERIENCED
AND, MIGHT I BOAST,
SUPERIOR DIGIMON?
TAI, SORRY.
PLEASE PERMIT ME
TO PRESENT MY FELLOW ACTORS
IN THIS CAPTIVATING AND CHARMING
COMEDY OF ERRORS...
HUH?
METALSEADRAMON...
[ METALSEADRAMON
LAUGHS EVILLY ]
MACHINEDRAMON...
[ GROWLS ]
PUPPETMON...
[ PUPPETMON LAUGHS ]
Puppetmon: YOU THOUGHT
YOU WERE THROUGH WITH ME,
BUT I WANTED
TO HAVE SOME MORE FUN.
AND MYSELF -- PIEDMON.
WE'D LIKE TO BEGIN BY ASKING
FOR AUDIENCE VOLUNTEERS.
WHO WOULD LIKE TO BE
THE FIRST TO BE DESTROYED?
OH, COME NOW. DON'T TELL ME
YOU HAVE STAGE FRIGHT.
I DIDN'T EVEN WANT TO GO
TO CAMP IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I JUST WANTED
TO GO TO THE MALL.
CAN'T SOMEBODY ELSE SAVE
THIS SILLY WORLD BESIDES ME?
MIMI.
I WANT TO BE A NORMAL KID
AND NOT HAVE ANY
BIG RESPONSIBILITIES.
IS THAT TOO MUCH TO ASK?
IT'S NOT FAIR!
OH! YOUR INCESSANT WHINING
IS GETTING ON MY NERVES.
YOU WILL BE
THE FIRST ONE TO GO.
AAH!
OHH.
[ GASPS ]
CHUMON, SPEAK TO ME,
YOU POOR THING.
MIMI, IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO BE DELETED.
[ SIGHS ]
CHUMON!
Piedmon: CHUMON WAS A FOOL.
OH, CHUMON!
Piedmon: NOW THAT HE'S
OUT OF THE WAY,
WHO WOULD LIKE TO BE
THE NEXT ONE
TO MAKE THEIR GRAND EXIT?
PIEDMON, YOU'RE GOING
TO BE WASHED UP
WHEN WE'RE
THROUGH WITH YOU.
BE MY GUEST.
PIX BOMB!
HEY, PIXIMON,
PERFECT TIMING.
I MISSED YOU.
PRODIGIOUS.
YOU CLEVERLY USED A BARRIER
TO AVOID DETECTION.
I SURE DID.
BUT YOU SAID IT WAS POSSIBLE
TO SAVE THE PLANET
IF THE EIGHT OF US
WERE ALL TOGETHER.
HOW COME
IT'S NOT HAPPENING?
THE TRUTH IS BEING TOGETHER
IS NOT ENOUGH.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
THAT YOU NEED TO DO TO BEAT HIM.
HOW ARE WE GOING
TO FIND OUT?
YEAH, ENOUGH RIDDLES.
THIS IS SOMETHING YOU
WILL DISCOVER ON YOUR OWN.
[ SCREAMING ]
AHA! HERE YOU ARE.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
I'LL TRY TO STOP THEM.
MAKE A RUN FOR IT
AND CLIMB TO THE TOP
OF SPIRAL MOUNTAIN,
BUT YOU BETTER MOVE IT.
YOU CAN'T STOP THEM.
THEY'RE ALL MEGADIGIMON.
I KNOW I CAN'T WIN,
BUT I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO DISTRACT THEM LONG ENOUGH
FOR YOU TO GET AWAY.
I'LL STAY WITH YOU.
NO WAY! BESIDES, WE NEED YOU
ON SPIRAL MOUNTAIN.
RIVER OF POWER!
PLEASE GO NOW.
YOU HAVE AN IMPORTANT TASK
AHEAD OF YOU.
ONCE YOU SUCCEED,
NO ONE WILL EVER BE ABLE
TO STOP YOU AGAIN.
I KNOW YOU WILL ALL
MAKE ME PROUD OF YOU.
Augumon: HE'S STRONGER
THAN HE LOOKS.
Tai: HE'LL HAVE TO BE
Kari: DO YOU THINK
IT'S POSSIBLE HE CAN DO IT?
Agumon: I DON"T KNOW, KARI.
I HOPE SO.
[ GRRRRR! ]
Piedmon: HOW CAN SUCH
A POWERLESS LITTLE DIGIMON
EVEN THINK ABOUT
DEFEATING US?
JUST CALL ME A CRAZY LITTLE
DIGIMON.
WILL PIXIMON HOLD OFF
THE DARK MASTERS
LONG ENOUGH
FOR THE DIGIDESTINED
TO REACH SPIRAL MOUNTAIN?
WATCH THE NEXT
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS."