♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGI ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE
THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Boy: THAT'S HOME,
PLANET EARTH.
BUT I'M NOT SURE THAT'S
WHERE I AM RIGHT NOW.
OK, LET ME BACK UP A LITTLE.
IT ALL BEGAN WHEN THE CLIMATE
WENT COMPLETELY OUT OF CONTROL.
THE RAIN FORESTS DRIED OUT,
AND OTHER PLACES GOT TOTALLY
FLOODED WITH OCEANS
LIKE CHOCOLATE SAUCE.
AND GET THIS--
CITIES WHICH WERE NORMALLY
BLAZING HOT IN THE SUMMER
GOT SUPER COLD.
AT THE TIME, I DIDN'T KNOW
ANY OF THIS WAS GOING ON
BECAUSE I WAS AT CAMP.
ALL OF THE OTHER CAMPERS WERE,
YOU KNOW, GOOFING OFF
AND HANGING OUT.
[SNORING]
ME? I WAS ENJOYING
THE SUMMER SUN
[SNORING]
WHILE GOING OVER
MY MULTIPLICATION TABLES.
THAT IS, UNTIL IT
STARTED TO SNOW...
IN THE MIDDLE OF JULY.
TOTALLY FREAKY.
AND IT GETS WEIRDER.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE WHAT HAPPENED
TO ME AND 6 OTHER KIDS.
OH, BY THE WAY,
MY NAME'S TAI.
[GASPS]
THIS IS SORA.
SHE'S OK...FOR A GIRL.
AND MATT...
MATT'S TOO COOL.
JUST LOOK AT THAT HAIRCUT.
AND THIS LITTLE KID
IS IZZY.
HE SHOULD'VE GONE
TO COMPUTER CAMP.
THAT'S MIMI.
I'LL BET YOU CAN GUESS
HER FAVORITE COLOR
ON THE FIRST TRY.
T.K. IS MATT'S
DOPEY LITTLE BROTHER.
OH, AND THIS IS JOE,
BUT DON'T EVER SCARE HIM.
HE'D PROBABLY WET HIS PANTS.
[LAUGHING]
COLD.
Tai: THERE WE ALL WERE
IN CAMP, WHEN SUDDENLY,
THIS HUGE BLIZZARD
CAME OUT OF NOWHERE.
NEEDLESS TO SAY,
THE CANOE RACES WERE CANCELED.
SO LET'S HAVE
TOBOGGAN RACES INSTEAD!
[LAUGHS]
I'M GONNA BUILD
THE BIGGEST SNOWMAN.
HEY, T.K.,
BE CAREFUL.
SLOW DOWN.
BRRR. IT IS FREEZING.
AND I DIDN'T
BRING A JACKET.
MAN, I WAS WORRIED
I'D CATCH A SUMMER COLD,
BUT THIS IS EVEN WORSE.
OH, WOW.
WHY DIDN'T I PACK
MY FLUFFY
PINK SNOW BOOTS?
STILL NOT WORKING.
BUMMER.
THIS STORM'S MAKING A MESS
OF MY INFRARED
INTERNET CONNECTION.
[GASPS]
LOOK IT.WOW.
HEY, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
IZZY!
COME ON OUT HERE.
YOU GOTTA SEE THIS.
WHOA.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
MAGICAL EVEN.
YEAH.
YEAH...BUT WHAT IS IT?
MAYBE AN AURORA?
YOU MEAN
AURORA BOREALIS,
THE NORTHERN LIGHTS?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
YOU SEE THAT IN ALASKA.
WE'RE WAY TOO FAR SOUTH.
TELL THAT
TO THE SNOW.
I REALLY THINK WE OUGHT
TO GET BACK INSIDE
BEFORE WE ALL COME DOWN
WITH PNEUMONIA.
AND MISS THIS?
THE SKY IS, LIKE,
SHORT-CIRCUITING.
HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
[GASPS]
[GASP]
AAH!
UH-OH!
DO YOU THINK
WE NEED SUNSCREEN?
AH.
AAH!
[SCREAMING]
EVERYONE,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
AH.
WE'RE STILL HERE.
THAT WAS SCARY.
WHAT--WHAT WAS IT?
METEORS?
OH...
OK, SO IT'S
NOT METEORS.
HUH?
WHAT...ARE THESE?
MY GUESS
IS SOME SORT OF
MINIATURE REMOTE
DIGITAL APPARATUS.
NO INSTRUCTIONS?
FORGET THE INSTRUCTIONS.
SURF'S UP!
[SCREAMS]
WHOA!
AAH!
Mimi: I KNEW
I SHOULD HAVE GONE
TO CHEERLEADING CAMP!
Koromon: TAI?
YOO-HOO, TAI.
YEAH, I'M OK.
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
THAT IS THE LAST TIME
I EAT CAMP FOOD.
HEY, YOU DON'T NEED
TO BE AFRAID OF ME.
I'M YOUR FRIEND!
UH, JUST WHAT ARE YOU?
HAVE YOU HAD
YOUR RABIES SHOTS?
[LAUGHS]
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE
ALL RIGHT NOW, TAI.
I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR YOU.
WAITING FOR ME?
MY NAME'S KOROMON.
AND WE'RE PARTNERS.
KOROMON?
THAT MEANS...
TALKING HEAD?
HMM. IT MEANS BRAVE
LITTLE WARRIOR.
AND DON'T
FORGET IT, TAI.
SO WHAT DID YOU MEAN,
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR ME?
AND HOW DID YOU
KNOW MY NAME?
TAI?
HMM? IZZY, THAT YOU?
IT'S ME.
AND I'VE GOT THIS
LITTLE PINK THING
FOLLOWING ME EVERYWHERE.
IT IS ME, MOTIMON,
AT YOUR SERVICE.
ANYBODY WANT LUNCH?
AH!
ANOTHER ONE?
WHAT ARE THEY?
OH.
ALLOW ME TO
INTRODUCE MYSELF.
MY FRIENDS
CALL ME MOTIMON.
EVERYONE DOES,
ACTUALLY.
I BELIEVE THOSE MINIATURE
REMOTE DIGITAL GADGETS
HAVE TAKEN ON
AN ACTUAL LIFE FORM.
I DON'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING LIKE THIS
IN THE CAMP BROCHURE.
YA THINK?
IT'S WEIRD.
THE VEGETATION IS LUSH,
BUT THE SOIL APPEARS
RATHER COMMON.
Motimon: NOTHING IS
COMMON IN DIGIWORLD.
Koromon:
THAT'S RIGHT, TAI.
YOU ARE IN
THE DIGIWORLD.
AND JUST WHERE IS
THE DIGIWORLD?
OH, I DON'T CARE SO MUCH
ABOUT WHERE IT IS.
I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT IT IS.
GUESS I'LL JUST
TAKE A LOOK AROUND
FOR MYSELF.
THE OCEAN?
WHAT'S THAT DOING THERE?
OUR CAMPSITE WAS
NOWHERE NEAR THE OCEAN.
AND I SURE
DON'T REMEMBER
THOSE MOUNTAINS.
HMM. SOMETHING TELLS ME
A COMPASS ISN'T
GONNA HELP MUCH.
HEY, TAI.
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
NOTHING I RECOGNIZE.
HUH? WAIT.
WHAT'S THAT?
LOOK AT THAT.
IT'S SOME SORT OF
GIANT RED BEETLE.
AND IT'S FLYING
RIGHT AT US. AAH.
AAH! I CAN'T WATCH.
THAT IS ONE
SERIOUSLY BAD DIGIMON,
EVEN WHEN
HE'S IN A GOOD MOOD.
THAT'S JUST GREAT.
WATCH OUT!
HUH?
HIS NAME IS KUWAGAMON.
HE'S AN INSECTOID
DIGIMON.
VICIOUS AND RUTHLESS,
WITH TEETH LIKE KNIVES
AND SCISSOR-HANDS
THAT CAN CHOP THROUGH
ANYTHING.
WHO NEEDS A GARDENER?
HANG ON!
WHOA!
UGH!
TAI, YOU OK?
WELL, I HAVE
HAD BETTER DAYS.
AAH!
AAH.
LITTLE GUY.
YOU SHOULD PICK ON BUGS
YOUR OWN SIZE.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME? KOROMON?
THAT'S ME.
YOU'RE PRETTY BRAVE...
FOR A LITTLE GUY.
I'M IMPRESSED.
HEH HEH.
IT WAS NOTHIN'.
UH, TAI, HE'S HEADING
THIS WAY AGAIN.
OH, DEAR, OH, DEAR!
QUICKLY, EVERYONE!
THIS WAY!
COME ON!
HURRY UP!
FOR HAVING
2 LONG LEGS,
YOU BOYS ARE
AWFULLY SLOW.
INSIDE THIS TREE.
LET'S GO!
WHOA.
WHAT KIND OF TREE
IS THIS?
IT'S A HIDING TREE,
SILLY.
QUIET NOW.
DON'T MAKE A SOUND.
HUH?
Sora: ALL CLEAR.
NO NEED TO HIDE ANYMORE!
SORA!
YOU CAN COME OUT NOW.
OH, WE WERE JUST
PLANNING THE TRAP
WE WERE GONNA SET
FOR THAT BIG BUG.
[GASPS]
[PURRING]
I AM ENCHANTED TO MEET YOU,
FRIENDS OF SORA. WELCOME.
TAI, IZZY, MEET YOCOMON.
MY OWN PERSONAL
SOMETHING-OR-OTHER.
LOOKS KIND OF
LIKE A RADISH.
MUST BE ANOTHER
ONE OF THEM.
LIKE THE OTHER--
WHATEVER
THEY ARE.
UH-OH.
[GASPS]
THEY'RE POPPING UP
EVERYWHERE.
HELLO! I AM TOKOMON.
HEY, T.K.! OVER HERE!
COMING!
TOKOMON!
THERE YOU ARE!
T.K.!
HEY, MATT.
YOU, TOO?
YEAH. I'M HERE, TOO.
NO. I MEANT THAT,
UNDER YOUR ARM.
OH. THIS GUY?
YEAH, WELL...
HELLO. YOU APPEAR
PLEASANT.
TSUNOMON IS MY NAME,
AND I AM QUITE
PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
[GIGGLING]
HELP!
AAH!
JOE?
HELP ME!
THIS THING! THIS THING!
IT WON'T LEAVE ME ALONE!
HEY, WHO ARE YOU
CALLING A THING?
I'M NO
STUFFED ANIMAL.
THE NAME
IS BUKAMON.
[SCREAMS]
[LAUGHS]
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU GUYS?
DON'T YOU SEE THIS CREATURE
HANGING OFF ME?
AND THOSE CREATURES
STANDING RIGHT THERE--
AAH!
THEY'RE--
THEY'RE EVERYWHERE!
WHAT ARE THEY?
WE'RE...
All: DIGIMON!
DIGITAL MONSTERS!
DIGITAL MONSTERS?
YES. DIGIMON!
Koromon: WE'RE NOT
JUST DIGITAL MONSTERS.
WE'RE MUCH MORE THAN THAT.
WE'RE...KINDA CUTE.
AND VERY LOYAL.
WITH BEAUTIFUL HAIR.
OR MAYBE
NO HAIR AT ALL.
WE CAN BE FUNNY. HA!
AND ADORABLE.
IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET EACH OF YOU.
MY NAME'S TAI,
AND THESE ARE
MY FRIENDS FROM CAMP.
I'D LIKE TO MEET SORA.
NICE PLACE YOU GOT HERE.
EXCEPT THE BUGS.
AND THE SELF-PROCLAIMED
COOL ONE OVER THERE
IS MATT.
NO AUTOGRAPHS,
PLEASE.
AND THIS IS JOE.
I'D SHAKE HANDS
IF YOU HAD ANY.
IZZY HERE IS OUR
COMPUTER EXPERT.
DO YOU HAVE
INTERNET ACCESS?
AND LAST,
BUT NOT LEAST,
THIS LITTLE GUY
IS, UH...
T.K. CALL ME T.K.
AND I'M NOT AS
SMALL AS I LOOK.
THERE NOW.
IS THAT EVERYBODY?
HEY, WHAT HAPPENED
TO THAT GIRL
WITH THE FUNNY PINK HAT?
NOW, NOW.
HER NAME IS MIMI.
WELL, PERHAPS SHE'S
OFF PICKING FLOWERS
OR GOING ON
A NATURE HIKE OR--
[SCREAMING]
SOMEBODY HELP ME!
COME ON!
OK, SO SHE'S NOT
PICKING FLOWERS.
MIMI!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
AAH!
THERE SHE IS.
MIMI, IT'S OK.
[GASPS]
AAH!
IT'S THAT BIG BUG AGAIN.
MIMI, ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT?
THINK SO.
DON'T WORRY.
TANEMON'S HERE
TO PROTECT YOU.
IT'S OK NOW.
OH, SORA.
WATCH IT.
HERE HE COMES!
RUN!
DOWN!
[GASP] WILL THIS
NIGHTMARE NEVER END?
AAH!
MY MOM IS GONNA WANT
A COMPLETE AND TOTAL REFUND.
HERE HE COMES AGAIN!
OK, THAT DOES IT!
NO MORE RUNNING AWAY!
WHAT ELSE CAN WE DO?
SHE'S RIGHT.
THERE'S NO WAY WE CAN
FIGHT THAT THING.
NOT AND WIN, ANYWAY.
[ALL GASP]
GREAT. ANYBODY
BRING A HELICOPTER?
BE CAREFUL, TAI.
THERE'S NO WAY DOWN.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO FIND ANOTHER WAY.
ANOTHER WAY WHERE?
[SCREAMING]
AAH!
WATCH OUT, TAI!
HERE I GO!
OH!
NOT AGAIN!
DIGIMON, ATTACK!
Sora: YOCOMON!
YOCOMON!
KOROMON,
ARE YOU CRAZY?
WHY'D YOU DO IT?
SORRY. IT'S JUST...
I'M TRYING TO MAKE
A GOOD IMPRESSION.
CRAZY GUY.
OHH...
YOCOMON.
TANEMON.
TALK TO ME.
THEY MUST BE PROGRAMMED
FOR COURAGE.
TOKOMON,
WHAT'S WRONG?
HEY, TSUNOMON,
WAKE UP.
BUKAMON, WAKE UP.
[KUWAGAMON ROARING]
HUH?
OH, NO!
Matt: GET BACK!
Sora: I WAS HOPING
WE'D SEEN THE LAST OF HIM.
ME, TOO.
GUESS HE HAD
OTHER PLANS, HUH?
Tai: AHH, I KNEW I SHOULD'VE
BROUGHT MY BUG SPRAY.
OK, GET READY TO RUN.
NO, WE FIGHT.
HUH?
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
STAND AND FIGHT.
GIVE IT UP,
WILL YA?
NO, KOROMON'S RIGHT.
IT'S TIME THAT WE SHOWED
WHAT WE'RE MADE OF.
NO, DON'T!
THEY'RE RIGHT.
NO WAY.
IT'S HOPELESS.
YOU'RE NO MATCH
FOR HIM, YOCOMON.
WE CAN DO IT. LET ME GO,
LET ME GO, LET ME GO...
YES, WE CAN DO IT,
WE CAN DO IT.
LET ME GO, LET ME GO,
LET ME GO!
TANEMON, YOU, TOO?
UH-HUH.
I'M SORRY, TAI.
AAH! LET'S GO!
COME ON, DIGIMON!
IT'S USELESS!
YOCOMON!
DON'T GO!
MOTIMON!
NO, WAIT!
DON'T DO IT,
TSUNOMON!
DON'T GO!
AAH!
TURN AROUND!
COME BACK, BUKAMON!
TANEMON!
BE CAREFUL!
NO! DON'T!
KOROMON!
COME BACK!
[GASPS]
KOROMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
AGUMON!
YOCOMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
BIYOMON!
MOTIMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
TENTOMON!
TSUNOMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
GABUMON!
TOKOMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
PATAMON!
BUKAMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
GOMAMON!
TANEMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
PALMON!
Sora: WHAT IN THE--
LOOK AT THEM!
WHAT'S HAPPENED
TO THE LITTLE GUYS?
THEY'RE BIGGER.
HI-YAH!
ALL RIGHT, THEN!
YOU ASKED FOR IT!
POISON IVY!
BOOM BUBBLE!
SUPER SHOCKER!
STAND BACK, EVERYONE!
PEPPER BREATH!
BLUE BLASTER! PAAH!
SPIRAL TWISTER! RAAH!
NOW ALL TOGETHER!
[GASPS]
WOW.
THEY MADE VAPORWARE
OUT OF HIM.
AMAZING.
TOLD YOU
WE COULD DO IT.
[LAUGHS]
[LAUGHS] KOROMON!
OR AGUMON OR
WHOEVER YOU ARE!
YOU DID IT! YOU DID IT!
YOU DID IT!
HOW ABOUT THAT
SUPER SHOCKER?
PRETTY WIZARD, HUH?
[GASPS] WATCH OUT!
HUH?
GUESS WE CELEBRATED
TOO SOON.
AAH!
[SCREAMING]
Tai: SO, JUST WHEN WE MAKE
SOME PRETTY COOL FRIENDS,
WE ALL TAKE A PLUNGE...
NEVER TO SEE
EACH OTHER AGAIN?
I DON'T THINK SO...
BUT FIND OUT
FOR YOURSELF...
NEXT TIME ON DIGIMON.
DIGITAL MONSTERS.