Gomamon:
AFTER DEVIMON DESTROYED
VILE ISLAND, MATT AND I WERE STRANDED
IN A FREEZING ENVIRONMENT.
ON ANOTHER ISLAND,
TAI AND AGUMON
ENCOUNTERED FRIGIMON,
A VICTIM OF THE BLACK GEARS.
THEY GOT FRIGIMON
BACK TO HIS KIND SELF.
IN GRATITUDE HE CREATED
A BRIDGE TO OUR ISLAND.
WHEN WE FOUND EACH OTHER,
THINGS WENT BADLY
BETWEEN MATT AND TAI.
THEY GOT EVEN WORSE
WHEN MOJIMON ATTACKED.
AGUMON AND I DIGIVOLVED
AND DEFEATED MOJIMON.
I DO HOPE WE
FIND ALL THE OTHERS SOON.
♪ DI-DI-DI,
DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE INTO
DIGITS OF CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE-- ♪
♪ ( bird cry ) ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
WHOA! TENTOMON,
I WOULD SAY WE ARE TRAVELLING
AT A VERY HIGH SPEED,
PLUMMETING TOWARD
AN UNIDENTIFIED ISLAND.
AND, UH,
CRASH LANDING IS IMMINENT.
Tentemon:
TRY TO THINK OF IT AS
WE'RE JUST HITTING THE BEACH!
( screaming )
Mimi:
NOW THAT SHOULD BE GOOD
FOR SOME FREQUENT-FLYER MILES!
Palmon:
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH NO--HUMIDITY!
SOME KIND OF TROPICAL RAIN
FOREST,
BUT NOT ONE
I'M FAMILIAR WITH.
IT ALL HAPPENED SO FAST--
WHERE ARE WE?
HAVE YOU ANY IDEA
WHAT HUMIDITY DOES TO MY HAIR?
IT GOES ALL POODLE-Y!
NOT A PRETTY SIGHT.
PERHAPS WE OUGHT TO
LOOK FOR THE OTHERS.
YEAH, LET'S GO--
MAYBE WE CAN FIND
SOME AIR CONDITIONING.
Tentomon:
HERE WE ARE, IZZY--
HARDLY THE LIGHT AND BREEZY
LODGINGS I WAS EXPECTING.
WHOA...
VERY INTERESTING,
BUT DON'T YOU THINK
WE SHOULD KEEP SEARCHING
FOR THE OTHERS?
NOW REALLY ISN'T THE TIME--
I KNOW,
BUT LOOK AT THIS PLACE!
IT'S PRODIGIOUS--
I GOTTA CHECK IT OUT.
ALL RIGHT,
BUT JUST FOR A MINUTE.
Mimi:
YUM! BANANAS!
BANANA?
CAN YOU REACH
HIGH ENOUGH?
UM-HMM.
I WAS REALLY STARVED!
NOW WE CAN PRETEND
WE'RE HAVING BANANA SPLITS.
HUH?
WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?
THEY CERTAINLY DO
LOOK DELICIOUS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
THIS PLACE IS SERIOUSLY
GETTING ON MY NERVES.
HMM?
IS THAT HAIR MOUSSE?
YUK!
HUH?
DUH, GOODBYE!
MEET TO NICE YA.
HE MEANS HELLO,
NICE TO MEET YA.
YEAH, WHAT HE'S SAYING.
ME MEANS I'M RIGHT.
PALMON,
WHO'S THE TALKING DESSERT?
IT'S SUKAMON AND CHUUMON,
ALSO KNOWN AS THE DIGI-LOSERS.
HEY! THANKS!
Palmon:
THEY'RE ALWAYS TOGETHER
BECAUSE THEY SHARE
THE SAME BRAIN--
AND IT'S NOT A VERY BIG ONE.
YAAH!
( goofy laughter )
WAIT!
LEAVE US ALONE!
OKAY--BUT FIRST YOU GOTTA PAY
A WHATTAYA-CALL-IT.
A TOLL.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN A TOLL?
DOES SHE THINK SHE CAN USE
OUR WOODS FOR FREE?
SHE'S GOTTA PAY--
THAT PURSE WOULD DO.
I LIKE THE HAT!
NO!
HUH?
WHAT PART OF "NO"
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
GET OUT OF HERE!
I THINK SHE INSULTED US.
BINGO, EINSTEIN.
SHE DID?
LET HER HAVE IT!
DO IT AGAIN!
( laughing moronically )
I GIVE UP--I WANT TO SEE
THE CAMP THERAPIST.
Sukamon:
OH, PRETTY...
Chuumon:
WOW! THAT'S BETTER THAN
CHEWING TIN FOIL!
I FEEL ALL TINGLY AND REFRESHED
LIKE A WHOLE NEW PERSON!
YEAH!
IS THIS ONE AS MUCH OF A PAIN
AS THE LAST ONE?
NO, REALLY--
WE'LL BE NICE FROM NOW ON!
SO YOU'LL LEAVE
US ALONE?
BUT FIRST TELL US IF YOU'VE SEEN
ANY OTHER HUMANS AROUND HERE.
ANY WHAT?
CREATURES THAT
LOOK LIKE THIS ONE.
AS A MATTER OF FACT...
DUH...
YEAH, I FORGOT!
TELL ME!
IT WASN'T NEARLY AS PRETTY
AS YOU ARE,
BUT WE SAW SOMETHING FALL INTO
THE RUINS WITH TENTOMON.
WHEN WERE YOU GONNA TELL US--
NEXT WEEK?
THEY MUST HAVE
SEEN IZZY, TOO!
CAN YOU TAKE US THERE?
IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT WE FIND THEM.
OKIE-DOKIE.
NO FUNNY BUSINESS!
CROSS OUR HEARTS--
AND HOPE TO DIE.
OF ALL THE RIDICULOUS
THINGS TO SAY!
Sukamon:
RIGHT-OVER-THERE!
Mimi:
HUH?
OH, THAT'S JUST GREAT.
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO
GET OVER THERE?
Chuumon:
WHY DON'T YOU
THINK OF SOMETHING?
A GORGEOUS GIRL LIKE YOU
MUST HAVE A BIG BRAIN!
THANKS A LOT.
BEFORE YOU GO,
GIVE US A THANK-YOU KISS, HUH?
( kissy sounds )
PLEASE TELL ME
THEY'RE KIDDING!
CLIMB ABOARD, QUICKLY!
OH...MAYBE WE JUMPED THE GUN.
BLEECH! JUST THE THOUGHT OF IT
IS MAKING ME QUEASY.
THAT'S OKAY!
WE'LL WAIT TILL YOU COME BACK!
DON'T HOLD YOUR BREATH.
( raspberry )
Tentomon:
IZZY, I HIGHLY SUGGEST WE END
THIS ARCHITECTURAL TOUR.
AS I MENTIONED BEFORE,
I'M GATHERING INFORMATION.
I'M SURE THIS PLACE
IS CRAWLING WITH CLUES.
LOOK! IT'S ONE OF
DEVIMON'S BLACK GEARS!
SO IT IS.
KNOW WHAT I THINK?
IF WE KEEP THIS GEAR
FROM TURNING,
WE'LL JAM THAT CREEP UP!
OR BETTER, WE COULD NOT
DO THAT,
AND LOOK FOR THE OTHERS,
LIKE WE SHOULD HAVE DONE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
WAIT A MINUTE--
THIS IS THE SAME WRITING
WE SAW THE LAST TIME.
REMEMBER?
IT MADE ME REALIZE
THAT IN DIGI-WORLD,
BASIC DATE IS
A LIVING, VIABLE SUBSTANCE.
ALL THAT DATA IS STORED
ON MY HARD DRIVE...
IF ONLY THERE WAS
A POWER SOURCE HERE.
GET A POWER SOURCE,
STOP THE GEAR--
IS "FIND OUR FRIENDS"
ON THAT LIST?
THOSE LIGHTS ARE GETTING
POWER FROM SOMEWHERE.
HEY, AN OUTLET!
CHECK IT OUT.
IT WORKS!
OH, GOODY.
NOW LET'S SEE
IF I CAN DECIPHER THIS.
( computer sounds )
Mimi:
WELL, HERE ARE THE RUINS.
LET'S JUST HOPE THAT
KISSY-FACE CUSTARD
WAS TELLING THE TRUTH.
ONE WAY TO FIND OUT!
OH!
HURRAY!
IT'S THEM!
TENTEMON AND IZZY!
HEY!
UH...HI, MIMI.
FINALLY A FRIENDLY FACE!
WHERE'S THE REST
OF THE GANG?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
BUT SHOULDN'T WE LIKE
LOOK FOR THEM OR SOMETHING?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
ANYWAY?
TRYING TO DECIPHER
THESE HIEROGLYPHS.
CAN'T THAT WAIT?
THAT'S WHAT I
KEEP TELLING HIM.
"LET'S LOOK FOR THE OTHERS,"
I SAY,
BUT DOES HE LISTEN?
NO.
IZZY, GET UP.
I'M SURE THE KEY TO FIGURING
EVERYTHING OUT IS IN HERE.
THE QUESTION IS,
DOES EACH GLYPH REPRESENT
A LETTER, A WORD, OR A PHRASE?
HMM....
I'LL HAVE TO CROSS-REFERENCE
THE CHARACTERISTICS.
( all sigh )
Mimi:
IZZY, ANY IDEA HOW LONG
THIS IS GOING TO TAKE?
I MEAN CAN WE GO
BEFORE WINTER SETS IN?
IZZY!
IZZY, YOUR FRIEND
IS ASKING YOU A QUESTION.
AND HER REAR END IS GETTING COLD
SITTING HERE DOING NOTHING.
WAIT--THAT MIGHT WORK!
UH-OH...IZZY!
ARE YOU IGNORING ME,
YOU COMPUTER GEEK?
( Izzy muttering to himself )
( sputtering )
HEY! HERE'S SOMETHING!
THESE RUINS ARE
A GIGANTIC MAZE!
I'M LEAVING!
RIGHT NOW!
BOO HOO HOO!
BOO HOO!
NOT YOU TOO!
IZZY--DO SOMETHING!
DO WHAT?
MY LAPTOP CAN'T DO EVERYTHING!
I DON'T KNOW--
TELL HER YOU'RE SORRY!
SORRY? FOR WHAT?
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE!
I'M STARVING
AND MY FEET ARE KILLING ME
AND A GIANT LEMON CUSTARD
TRIED TO KISS ME
AND ALL I WANT TO DO
IS GET OUT OF HERE!
HOW CAN YOU BE
SO INSENSITIVE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU IGNORE US WHILE YOU
POKE AWAY AT YOUR COMPUTER!
I'M NOT IGNORING YOU--
THIS IS ULTRA-IMPORTANT,
LIKE MAYBE SAVING THIS WORLD.
IF I CAN JUST
DECIPHER THESE HIERO--
JUST KEEP
YOUR STUPID HIEROGLYPHICS!
BOO HOO HOO!
MIMI, WAIT!
YOU THINK I'M JUST
PLAYING AROUND HERE?
I THINK YOU LIKE COMPUTERS
MORE THAN PEOPLE!
BOO HOO HOO!
Izzy:
DON'T LOOK NOW,
BUT MIMI AND TENTOMON ARE GONE.
NOW WHAT DO WE DO?
Mimi:
I HATE THIS PLACE!
I'LL NEVER RECOMMEND
THIS RESORT TO ANYONE!
MIMI, WAIT!
( thud )
OH, DEAR!
MIMI, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M NOT A BAD PERSON...
WHY IS ALL THIS
HAPPENING TO ME?
WE'VE GOT TO BE CAREFUL.
ONE WRONG TURN
AND WE COULD GET LOST IN HERE!
ALL I WANT TO DO IS GET HOME--
THAT'S ALL!
PLEASE WAIT--WE REALLY SHOULD
FIND OUR WAY BACK.
I WANT MY OWN BED,
MY OWN BATHROOM...
I'M EVEN STARTING
TO MISS MY BABY BROTHER!
STOP RUNNING OFF!
Palmon:
I DON'T SEE THEM ANYWHERE--
WHERE COULD THEY HAVE GONE?
THEY DIDN'T GO DEEPER
INTO THE MAZE, DID THEY?
THAT'D BE MY GUESS.
THESE DECIPHERED HIEROGLYPHS
TELL ME
THE INSIDE OF THESE RUINS
IS A GIANT LABYRINTH.
SO IF THAT'S THE CASE...
THEY COULD BE
LOST IN THERE FOREVER.
FOREVER? OH!
Mimi:
HEY, UH, TENTEMON...
Tentemon:
YES?
DO YOU GET THE FEELING
WE'RE GOING IN CIRCLES?
SEE THIS SMUDGE
ON THE WALL?
I REMEMBER PASSING IT
A LONG TIME AGO.
YOU'RE RIGHT!
COULD WE BE LOST?
THIS IS PROBABLY A BAD TIME
TO SAY "I TOLD YOU SO..."
OH, QUIET!
I CAN'T BEAR IT--
I'M GOING IN!
AND GET LOST TOO?
NO PALMON--
WE HAVE GOT TO USE OUR HEADS.
BUT WE CAN'T
JUST LEAVE THEM!
WE WON'T,
BUT THIS IS
A SUPER-COMPLICATED MAZE.
I'VE GOTTA TRY TO
GET A HANDLE ON IT.
THEN MAYBE I CAN
HELP GET THEM OUT.
Tentomon:
WELL, BEING LOST
ISN'T SO BAD.
OH DEAR--
ARE YOU HURT?
NO, I'M FINE,
I'M GETTING USED TO IT BY NOW.
IF I HAD JUST GONE TO
CHEERLEADING CAMP
NONE OF THIS
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED.
LET'S TRY A SYSTEMATIC APPROACH
TO THIS.
IF WE KEEP TURNING TO THE LEFT--
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT--
WHY SHOULD I LISTEN TO YOU?
IT'S YOUR FRIEND IZZY
THAT GOT ME INTO THIS MESS.
YES, HE GETS A LITTLE
WRAPPED UP IN HIS WORK
AND DOESN'T ALWAYS
INTERACT WELL WITH OTHERS,
BUT HE'S A GOOD BOY.
Izzy:
THERE THEY ARE!
THAT BLINKING LIGHT
IS MIMI?
PRECISELY.
Tentomon over the computer:
No, not that way!
Mimi:
Buzz off--leave me alone!
THAT'S MY GIRL!
I HOMED IN ON THE SIGNAL
FROM HER DIGI-VICE.
WE CAN HEAR HER--
LET'S HOPE SHE CAN HEAR US.
IZZY TO MIMI--
DO YOU READ ME?
Izzy:
Repeat--do you read me?
IZZY, IS THAT YOU?
ALL RIGHT! IT'S WORKING!
MIMI, I'M GONNA NAVIGATE
FOR YOU
SO WALK EXACTLY WHERE
I TELL YOU TO.
Mimi:
Uh...
DON'T WORRY--
IT'LL BE OKAY!
Tentomon:
IS THAT YOU, PALMON?
JUST FOLLOW IZZY'S DIRECTIONS
AND YOU'LL BE OUT OF THERE.
SEE? I TOLD YOU
IZZY WAS A GOOD BOY.
OKAY--TAKE THE FIRST DOORWAY
ON THE RIGHT.
WHEN YOU GET TO THE END,
TURN LEFT,
BUT BE CAREFUL OF THE NEXT ROOM,
THERE'S A BIG HOLE IN THE FLOOR.
Mimi:
OH!
AH!
Izzy:
There should be a narrow ledge
you can use to get across.
Mimi:
DID WE HAVE TO TAKE
THE SCENIC ROUTE?
( beeping )
UH-OH!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"UH-OH"?
OKAY, I'M READY--
WHICH WAY SHOULD WE GO?
Tentemon:
SOMETHING HAS HAPPENED.
Izzy:
I WAS HOPING IT WAS
JUST A GLITCH.
BUT THERE'S DEFINITELY SOMETHING
IN THAT MAZE WITH THEM
AND IT'S MOVING CLOSER.
NOW I AM
STARTING TO WORRY.
Mimi:
IZZY, WHAT'S WITH
THE SILENT TREATMENT?
( evil laughter )
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
IT SOUNDED EVIL!
Evil voice:
TENTEMON, IT'S BEEN
SUCH A LONG TIME.
Tentemon:
OH, NO!
CENTARUMON!
HALF MAN, HALF HORSE!
YOU REALLY DON'T WANT TO
GET ON EITHER OF HIS BAD SIDES!
( Mimi shrieks )
AHH!
Centarumon:
I LIKE A GOOD CHASE!
HANG A LEFT!
IZZY, WE QUITE ANXIOUSLY
AWAITING YOUR DIRECTIONS!
ARE YOU THERE?!
ANOTHER LEFT--
THROUGH THE DOORWAY!
THIS WAY, MIMI!
GREAT JOB, IZZY--
IT'S A DEAD END!
WHERE DO WE NOW,
IZZY?
Tentemon:
Izzy! Hello?
WE'VE LOST
CONTACT!
OH, REALLY?
HE'S BACK?
SOLAR RAY!
AH!
FIRE!
OH--LOOK AT MY SKIRT!
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
YOUR BRAVERY IS NOTED,
BUT THAT ALONE WILL NOT
GAIN YOU ANY MERCY.
MAKE YOURSELF BIGGER!
IF YOU MEAN
YOU WANT ME TO DIGIVOLVE,
I'M AFRAID
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HE MEANS
HE CANNOT PROTECT YOU.
SO YOU HAVE TO HOLD YOUR GROUND,
AND THAT IS TRULY IMPOSSIBLE.
STOP TALKING
AND GET GROWING!
IF I'M SEPARATED
FROM IZZY I CAN'T!
STOP THAT--
CAN'T YOU SEE I'M IN THE MIDDLE
OF SAYING SOMETHING?
( rumbling )
WHAT'S THAT RACKET?
( gasps )
Mimi:
IZZY!
GET OUT OF THERE!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
TELL ME TWICE!
( space sounds )
PALMON DIGIVOLVE INTO...
TOGEMON!!!
LEAVE MY FRIENDS ALONE!
GET BACK!
LEAVE THIS TO ME!
TENTEMON DIGIVOLVE INTO...
KABUTERIMON!!!
Mimi:
I FORGOT--
WHEN YOU GET BIGGER, YOU REALLY
GET BIGGER.
WATCH WHERE YOU STEP!
SORRY.
THAT'S ONE WAY
TO GET OUT OF THERE.
THIS IS NO TIME FOR US
TO START TAKING IT EASY.
LOOK WHO'S HERE!
YEAH...
I SEE HIM.
LEAVE THEM ALONE!
ELECTRO-SHOCKER!
I THINK IT'S TIME FOR...
NEEDLE SPRAY!
THAT FELT...INTERESTING.
ONE OF THOSE BLACK GEARS
FELL OUT OF HIS BODY!
( moaning )
WHERE AM I?
ARE YOU
A GOOD DIGIMON NOW?
WHAT?
THAT DEVICE ON YOUR BAG--
THIS?
Centarumon:
I HAVE SEEN IT BEFORE...
IT IS THE MYSTICAL SYMBOL
OF THE DIGIVICE.
THESE RUINS ARE ITS TEMPLE,
AND I AM ITS GUARDIAN.
WELL, IT CERTAINLY
LOOKS FAMILIAR.
THE DIGIVICE IS
A PRESERVER OF THE LIGHT,
A LAST DEFENSE
AGAINST THE DARKNESS
THAT THREATENS EXISTENCE.
REALLY?
I DIDN'T GET THAT,
BUT I'M STARTING TO THINK
THEY'RE MORE THAN JUST
A COOL ACCESSORY.
LEOMON! WHY ARE YOU HERE?
TO DESTROY THEM...
THE CHILDREN.
I WARN YOU, CENTARUMON,
DO NOT INTERFERE WITH ME.
( growling )
NO, LEOMON!
I CAN'T LOOK,
IT'S TOO SCARY!
WELL, MAYBE A PEEK.
Izzy:
WHOA--TIME'S STANDING STILL!
I SAID NO, LEOMON!
THE CHILDREN
POSSESS THE DIGIVICE!
AS GUARDIAN OF ITS TEMPLE,
I MUST PROTECT THEM AS WELL!
PROTECT THEM FROM ME?
GOOD LUCK!
FIST OF THE BEAST KING!
SOLAR RAY!
NOW LET'S STOP THIS MADNESS
BEFORE ONE OF US IS HURT.
LEOMON?
UGH!
THE CHILDREN MUST BE...
DESTROYED.
( whimpering )
NO! YOU MUST MEAN
SOME OTHER CHILDREN!
HUH?
YOUR DIGIVICE--
IT STOPPED HIM IN HIS TRACKS!
Mimi:
BAD KITTY! OUT!
AARRRGGGH!!
( roaring )
( grunting )
WELL, THAT GOT RID
OF HIM.
THESE THINGS REALLY ARE
KIND OF AMAZING.
"A PRESERVER OF LIGHT
AGAINST THE DARKNESS."
CAN YOU ORDER
A PIZZA WITH IT?
Izzy:
CENTARUMON,
MAYBE WITH YOUR HELP
WE COULD STOP THIS BLACK GEAR.
NO, I'M AFRAID I HAVE
NEITHER THE STRENGTH
NOR THE KNOWLEDGE
TO OPPOSE DEVIMON
AND THE POWERS OF DARKNESS.
ARE YOU FINISHED?
WE NEED TO START LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING TO EAT.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO KEEP
DECIPHERING AND ANALYZING
THESE TWO SETS
OF HIEROGLYPHS.
I'M SURE ALL THE ANSWERS
ARE IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
EXCUSE ME,
ISN'T THIS WHERE I CAME IN?
YOU'RE NOT SERIOUSLY
STARTING ALL THAT AGAIN...
JUST A NANO.
THIS BLACK GEAR...
WHO CARES ABOUT
THAT DUMB OLD THING?
ALL I WANT IS LUNCH!
( all gasping )
Izzy:
LOOK! THE PROCESS
HAS REVERSED ITSELF!
Mimi:
AMAZING!
EXCELLENT WORK, MIMI.
SOMETIMES THE SIMPLEST SOLUTION
IS ACTUALLY THE BEST.
GREAT COMPLIMENT.
HIYA--I KNEW
YA COULDN'T KEEP AWAY.
OH!
Sukamon:
SO WE GONNA
GO ON A DATE OR WHAT?
COME ON!
WHAT'S YOUR PHONE NUMBER?
MAN, HE IS PERSISTENT.
Sukamon:
BLOW US A KISS!
OKAY...( raspberry )
Sukamon:
COME ON, DO IT
LIKE YOU MEAN IT!
YOU LIKE US,
YOU KNOW YOU DO...PLEASE?