Mimi:
AFTER LANDING IN THE FOREST,
PALMON AND I CROSSED OVER TO
ANOTHER FLOATING ISLAND,
WHERE WE FOUND
IZZY AND TENTOMON.
WHILE IZZY WAS BUSY
WITH HIS COMPUTER,
CENTARUMON--WITH A BLACK GEAR
STUCK IN HIM--ATTACKED!
IZZY SOMEHOW
STARTED TALKING TO ME
THROUGH MY DIGIVICE
AND LED US TO SAFETY.
WELL, ALMOST.
OUR LITTLE PARTNERS
DIGIVOLVED JUST IN TIME,
DRIVING OUT
THE BLACK GEAR.
LEOMON--STILL UNDER
DEVIMON'S CONTROL--APPEARED.
BUT WE USED OUR DIGIVICES
AND SHOOED THE BAD KITTY AWAY!
♪ DI-DI-DI,
DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE INTO
DIGITS OF CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE-- ♪
♪ ( bird cry ) ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
I, DEVIMON,
HAD COMPLETELY SEPARATED
THOSE SEVEN BRATS
AND THEIR PESTY DIGIMON.
THAT IS UNTIL
TAI AND MIMI
CAUGHT UP WITH MATT AND IZZY.
BUT I'LL MAKE SURE THEY
NEVER FIND THEIR OTHER FRIENDS.
ESPECIALLY WITH THE PLANS I HAVE
FOR SORA AND JOE
ON THAT LOVELY DAY,
THE BAKEMON HOLIDAY!
HA HA HA HA!
( evil laughter continues )
THERE'S ONE THING
I'VE LEARNED IN DIGIWORLD--
BEDS DON'T MAKE GOOD BOATS.
( Gomamon munching )
DID I JUST HEAR YOU
EATING AGAIN?
UH-HUH.
I TOLD YOU NOT TO EAT
ALL THE FOOD
SINCE WE DON'T KNOW
WHEN WE'LL FIND LAND!
WE NEED TO RATION,
MEANING TO SAVE FOOD FOR LATER--
AS IN MUCH LATER.
BUT IT IS, LATER,
YOU TOLD ME THAT 20 MINUTES AGO.
2O MINUTES IS NOT "MUCH LATER"!
PLEASE TELL ME THERE'S STILL
SOME FOOD IN THE BAG!
SINCE YOU CAN'T HANDLE BOATING
AND EATING AT THE SAME TIME,
I ATE IT ALL.
AND I NEED FOOD TO DIGIVOLVE
IN CASE WE RUN INTO BAD DIGIMON.
HAVE WE SEEN ANY BAD DIGIMON--
NO!
IF I STARVE,
WHO ARE YOU GONNA PROTECT?
WHA!
( retching )
THAT'S ENOUGH ABOUT FOOD.
( groans )
THINGS WILL GET BETTER SOON--
HANG IN THERE.
HUH?
THAT CRATE IS GONNA HIT US!
MAYBE IT'S FULL OF FRUIT,
VEGETABLES, BREAD, MILK, CEREAL,
HOT DOGS, COOKIES,
CANDY AND SODA!
I WISH.
WE WOULDN'T NEED MORE FOOD
IF YOU HADN'T EATEN OURS!
YOU'RE STRONG
WHEN YOU'RE HUNGRY.
STARVATION IS
A GOOD MOTIVATOR.
WE'LL NEED A JACKHAMMER
TO OPEN THIS.
HMM, LET'S SEE...
AARRGH!
AH!
ARRGGH!
OGRAMON!
RIGHT, YA LITTLE DIGI-PEST!
PUMMEL WHACK!
HA HA HA HA!
( whimpering )
EEE-YA!
HA HA HA!
COME OUT OF THE SEA,
MARCHING FISHES!
I'M NOT SCARED OF
SOME STINKIN' FISH!
ON SECOND THOUGHT,
THAT REALLY HURT!
WHAT POWERFUL FORCE
COULD CAUSE THIS EVIL DIGIMON
TO BE OUT-MUSCLED
BY A BUNCH OF SMALL FISH?
WHEN THE MEEK JOIN FORCES
TO FIGHT FOR A GOOD PURPOSE,
THEY CAN OFTEN BRING DOWN
THE POWERFUL.
AARRGGH!
THEN AGAIN, SOMETIMES
THEY HAVEN'T GOT A CHANCE.
AND NEITHER DO WE!
AND NOW FOR YOU "MEEKS"...
( teeth chattering with fear )
EEEEE-YAAAA!!
AAHHH!
( space sounds )
GOMAMON DIGIVOLVE INTO...
IKKAKUMON!!!
YOU'RE BIGGER NOW,
I'M SO SCARED...NOT!
HERE'S SOME HAND-TO-HAND
PUMMEL-WHACKING!
( blows landing )
HARPOON TORPEDO!
EEE-YA!
JOE, YOU'VE GOT TO
CLIMB UP ON MY BACK!
AARRGGH!
ARRGGH!
GO AHEAD AND RUN--
SEE HOW FAR YOU GET!
'FRAIDY-CATS,
COME BACK AND FIGHT!
I DARE YA!
OH, MAN,
I DON'T LIKE ADVENTURE--
I'M A STAY-AT-HOME-AND-READ
KIND OF GUY.
HUH?
I'M TIRED AND HUNGRY...
SINKING....
SINKING IS BAD.
IKKAKUMON,
WAIT A MINUTE--
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SOME SORT OF
SUPER WATER MAMMAL.
AAH!
( glub glub )
♪ SORA IS FISH-ING,
SORA IS FISH-ING ♪
CATCH ANYTHING?
NOT YET.
GIVE ME TIME
I'LL CATCH SOMETHING BIG.
I'D EVEN BE HAPPY
WITH A SARDINE.
I KNOW HOW HUNGRY
YOU CAN GET.
IF I CAUGHT A HUGE ANYTHING,
YOU'D BE RIGHT THERE EATING IT.
WELL, SINCE YOU
PUT IT THAT WAY...
DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU CAN MAKE A BIG CATCH?
LOOK! MAYBE THERE'S ONE NOW!
IT FEELS LIKE A WHALE--
THIS IS A WHOPPER FOR SURE!
Biyomon:
PULL HARDER!
I'M TRYING TO!
( grunting )
LET HE HELP!
UNGH!
HELP!
OH MY--THAT'S A PERSON!
JOE!
UUNNNGGH!
Gomamon:
THEN A LARGE CRATE
DRIFTED OVER TO US,
THEN OGRAMON POPPED OUT
AND ATTACKED US!
Sora:
HOW HORRIBLE!
IT WAS,
BUT I DIGIVOLVED
AND WE ESCAPED HIM,
BUT THEN MY STRENGTH LEFT ME.
I JUST COULDN'T SEEM TO
KEEP MY ENERGY UP.
THE NEXT THING I KNEW
I WAS SINKING DEEPER AND DEEPER.
WHEN I OPENED MY EYES
I FINALLY SPOTTED JOE NEARBY.
HE WAS UNCONSCIOUS
AND SINKING FAST.
I TRIED TO GET HIM
TO THE SURFACE,
BUT MY STRENGTH
WAS GIVING OUT AGAIN
AND I KNEW I COULDN'T
HOLD MY BREATH MUCH LONGER.
AND THAT'S ABOUT THE TIME
YOUR FISHING LINE HIT ME.
SO I GRABBED THAT LINE
AND WRAPPED IT AROUND JOE
AND HUNG ON UNTIL
YOU PULLED US IN.
Sora:
MY GOODNESS--!
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE BOTH OKAY.
BUT I'M WORRIED ABOUT JOE.
YOU ARE?
JOE'S GOING TO BE
JUST FINE.
PHYSICALLY, YES--BUT I'M WORRIED
ABOUT HIS CONFIDENCE.
FIGHTING OGRAMON BACK THERE
REALLY KNOCKED HIM OUT.
HE NEEDS TO REBUILD
HIS SELF-CONFIDENCE.
HOW CAN WE HELP HIM?
VERY SIMPLE--
WE JUST MAKE HIM OUR LEADER.
HUH?
HEY--WHERE'S OGRAMON?
HUH? HUH?
HE'S GONE, BUT WE'VE GOT
A BIGGER PROBLEM.
WE CAN'T FIND THE OTHERS--
WHAT SHALL WE DO?
WE'RE STUCK ON THIS ISLAND
WITH NO LEADER.
I GUESS YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
LEAD US, JOE.
WHAT?
I'M FOR HIM!
AND ME!
NOT ME--I AM NOT A LEADER.
YOU HAVE TO,
YOU'RE THE STRONGEST ONE HERE.
UM-HMM.
NOT TO MENTION
THE BRAVEST.
Gomamon:
COME ON, JOE--REMEMBER HOW
YOU FOUGHT THE UNIMON?
I AM BRAVE.
YOU'RE RIGHT--I AM
THE BRIGHTEST ONE HERE.
Sora:
LET'S NOT GET TOO
CARRIED AWAY.
OH.
BUT IF I FAIL,
WHO WILL SAVE YOU OR ME?
MY FISH LINE...HA HA.
HUH?
Joe:
DID YOU HEAR ANYTHING?
Sora:
YEAH, IT SEEMED TO COME
FROM UP THERE.
Biyomon:
WHAT DO YOU
SUPPOSE IT IS?
LOOKS KIND OF LIKE
A CHURCH.
WHEREVER THERE'S A CHURCH
THERE'S USUALLY PEOPLE.
MAYBE OUR FRIENDS!
SOMEONE SHOULD
CHECK IT OUT.
I'LL GO!
WAIT--JOE'S OUR LEADER NOW.
WHAT?
WELL, LEAD US.
WHAT IF WE SEE
A BAD DIGIMON?
I, UH...
I NEED A MOMENT.
OKAY.
Joe:
HUP, TWO, THREE, FOUR...
YOUR LEFT, TWO, THREE, FOUR...
Sora:
MUST YOU KEEP UP
THAT ARMY MARCH DRIVEL?
Joe:
HALT!
NOTICE ANYTHING?
Sora:
IT ALL LOOKS
SORTA FAMILIAR TO ME.
AS IF IN A DREAM,
OR DEJA VU--
YOU KNOW, LIKE WE'VE
BEEN HERE BEFORE.
YOU'RE RIGHT--
THIS LOOKS LIKE THE PART OF
THE ISLAND THAT BROKE WAY.
YEAH.
SO WE SHOULD FIND
OUR FRIENDS
OR SOME OTHER PEOPLE
TAKING SHELTER IN THAT CHURCH.
YOU'RE ASSUMING
QUITE A BIT THERE.
FINE! THAT'S MY OPINION!
I'M JUST GIVING YOU
ANOTHER VIEW.
I'M THE LEADER HERE!
EXCUSE ME.
MOVE OUT!
WOW.
WE'VE CREATED A MONSTER.
YOU THINK A BLACK GEAR
GOT HIM?
Joe:
STEP LIVELY, TROOPS,
LET'S HAVE NO STRAGGLERS.
THERE'S THE CHURCH.
WHO'S GOING IN?
WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
UH...
UH....
WHAT'S WRONG?
WELL, BOSS?
Gomamon:
JOE, YOU'RE THE LEADER.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO TAKE A PEEK?
NO, I DON'T WANT YOU
TAKING A PEEK!
I CAN'T WAIT
TO GO IN THERE.
Gomamon:
I THINK IT WORKED.
( all giggling )
OKAY, I'M AFRAID.
I WAS RIGHT--
JUST A NORMAL GROUP OF PEOPLE.
GUYS--WHOA!
THERE ARE
PEOPLE IN THE CHURCH--DANCING.
BADLY, I MIGHT ADD.
HUH?
Sora:
THERE ARE
PEOPLE.
THEY'RE DANCING,
AND THEY'RE WEARING MASKS.
LIKE IT'S...HALLOWEEN.
HALLOW...WHAT?
AH!
THEY'RE CELEBRATING
THE BAKEMON HOLIDAY. IT REMINDS ME OF HALLOWEEN!
Masked man:
WE'D LOVE TO HAVE YOU JOIN US--
WE DON'T GET MANY YOUNG PEOPLE
AND NO HOLIDAY IS COMPLETE
WITHOUT THEM.
YOU ARRIVED JUST IN TIME
FOR SOME....FUN.
Joe:
LIKE TRICK OR TREAT?
YOU DO THAT FOR BAKEMON?
YES.
"BAKEMON" AS IN "LORD BAKEMON?"
BUT THE ONLY BAKEMON
I KNOW OF IS A HORRIBLE DIGIMON
WHO LIVES AMONG GHOSTS
AS THEIR RULER.
WHY WOULD YOU HONOR
AND CELEBRATE SOMEONE LIKE THAT?
HE'S A LOSER!
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT!
DON'T YOU DARE COME IN HERE
TELLING US WHO TO HONOR!
BACK OFF!
Sora:
YOU'RE A LITTLE TOUCHY.
WE JUST WANT TO KNOW WHEN
THE TRICK OR TREATING STARTS.
YOU'RE NOT AFRAID?
All:
NO!
WELL, YOU SHOULD BE...
BECAUSE IT'S A TRICK!
All:
HUH?
AARRGGH! ENJOY THE TREAT!
AAH!
Gomamon:
THE MASKED MAN WAS
THE EVIL DIGIMON LORD BAKEMON.
NO ONE HAD EVER SEEN HIM
IN HIS TRUE FORM.
BAKEMON!
IT IS
TRICK--OR--TREAT!
( screaming )
Sora:
THE DANCERS!
WHO I BET ARE GHOSTS TOO!
All:
THAT'S RIGHT!
( ghosts wailing )
( kids and digimon screaming )
SPIRAL TWISTER!
GOMAMON DIGIVOLVED INTO...
GOMAMON!
I NEED FOOD--
YOU WERE RIGHT,
I SHOULD HAVE
SAVED SOME EARLIER.
BIYOMON, DIGIVOLVED INTO...
OH...
BIYOMON!
I'M HUNGRY TOO!
CAN'T DIGIVOLVE.
AH!
4( wailing )
Kids:
LET ME GO! HELP!
Ghost:
GET IN THERE!
HA HA HA!
All:
IT'S A TRICK,
YOU'RE THE TREAT....
OKAY, DON'T PANIC.
I'M STILL IN CONTROL
AND FEELING STRONG.
OKAY.
( tearfully: )
I DON'T WANNA BE
SOMEBODY'S APPETIZER!
I'M SUPPOSED TO
GO TO MED SCHOOL!
ADD PEPPER.
MORE?
WHY NOT.
AH-CHOO!
SALT AND PEPPER?
YOU'RE NOT REALLY GOING TO
EAT US, ARE YOU?
YOU'RE A LITTLE ON
THE SCRAWNY SIDE
BUT YOU'D BE SURPRISED WHAT
THE RIGHT SEASONINGS CAN DO.
YOU THINK WE CAN FINAGLE HIM
INTO DINING ON SOMEONE BIGGER?
WHAT KIND OF FIEND IS THIS GUY?
WHERE JUST KIDS!
Biyomon:
THERE MUST BE A WAY OUT OF HERE!
MAYBE WE'VE BEEN LOOKING
IN ALL THE WRONG PLACES.
THERE'S NOT MUCH ROOM
TO LOOK IN THIS PLACE.
HEY!
WHAT?
MAYBE WE CAN TRICK THE GUARD
AND ESCAPE.
I THINK THAT'S A GIVEN--
HE DOESN'T LOOK TOO SMART.
FIRST WE HAVE TO
TRY AND WAKE HIM UP.
HOW ARE WE GONNA DO THAT?
FOR A GHOST,
HE SLEEPS LIKE A LOG.
WE HAVE TO GET HIS ATTENTION
OR WE'LL NEVER ESCAPE.
BUT I'M ALL OUT OF IDEAS!
I THINK I HAVE
JUST THE THING.
AAH!
OOHHH!
HEY! WHAT'S THE IDEA?
WHEN DO YOU START?
START WHAT?
START TAUNTING US,
YOU FLOATING BAG O' WIND!
HUH?
YOU GIVE BAD DIGIMON
A BAD NAME.
BUT I HAVEN'T LEARNED
HOW TO TAUNT YET.
IT'S EASY!
JUST FIND OUT WHAT WE WANT,
THEN DON'T LET US HAVE IT.
HUH?
HERE'S HOW YOU TAUNT--
WE'RE STARVING,
SO YOU SHOW US FOOD BUT
DON'T GIVE US ANY--GOT IT?
I THINK I GOTCHA--
I'VE GOT SOME BANANAS.
THEN TAUNT IS WITH 'EM--
COME ON.
OKAY.
HOW'S THIS...
LOOKS GOOD, DOESN'T IT?
WE CAN'T SEE...
COME A LITTLE CLOSER.
HUH?
HERE?
YOU HAVE TO COME EVEN CLOSER
TO TAUNT US,
WE CAN'T REALLY SEE YOU.
YOU BET.
SEE?
HEY!
( struggling )
Gomamon:
THAT WAS A PRETTY GOOD IDEA.
NEVER GET BETWEEN A DIGIMON
AND HIS MEAL.
Joe:
YOU DON'T WANT TO EAT ME,
I'M MOSTLY GRISTLE, ANYWAY.
Sora:
ARE YOU SAYING
THEY SHOULD EAT ME FIRST?
CAN'T YOU SEE?
WE'RE BOTH FINISHED!
OH, GO HAVE YOUR PITY-PARTY
SOMEWHERE ELSE!
( chanting: )
MUNCHING YOU BOTH
WILL BE A TREAT!
AH!
All chanting:
WE'RE SCARY GHOSTS,
WE LIKE TO BOO,
NOW IT'S TIME TO CHEW ON YOU!
AAAH!
( space sounds )
GOMAMON DIGIVOLVE INTO...
IKKAKUMON!!!
( Joe and Sora screaming )
BIYOMON DIGIVOLVE INTO...
BIRDRAMON!!!
GREAT TIMING.
GO GET BAKEMON!
EEEE!
WHILE WE GET OUT OF HERE!!
AH!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
AARRGGH!
METEOR WING!
AAAH!
WHOA!
HE'S SURE PUTTING UP
A GOOD FIGHT!
LORD BAKEMON IS TOUGH!
ARRGGGH!
HIS POWER COMES FROM EVIL,
BUT I KNOW GOOD CAN BEAT HIM.
WHAT IF IT'S TOO LATE?
IT'S NEVER TOO LATE
TO FIGHT EVIL--
WE HAVE TO WEAKEN LORD BAKEMON
TO HELP OUR FRIENDS PREVAIL.
WE? YOU'RE THE LEADER,
NOT ME.
DON'T BE A QUITTER!
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
WE CAN BEAT HIM?
I ONCE SAW A SHOW
ABOUT THIS ROMAN PHYSICIST
WHO BELIEVED THAT REPEATING
A PHRASE
HELPS YOU FOCUS
MIND OVER MATTER.
LET'S FOCUS ON RUNNING!
NO--WE FOCUS ON MAKING BAKEMON
LOSE HIS POWER.
OKAY, YOU'RE IN CHARGE--
START FOCUSING.
BAKEMON, LOSE YOUR POWER,
BAKEMON, LOSE YOUR POWER...
JUMP IN ANY TIME...
WELL, HELP!!
ALRIGHT, BUT I DON'T KNOW,
IT'S JUST...
OH...
YEAH! WE'LL USE
MY LUCKY HAT!
BAKEMON LOSE YOUR POWER...
BAKEMON LOSE YOUR POWER,
(Joe continues chanting phrase )
BAKEMON IS GETTING WEAKER--
I BELIEVE IT'S WORKING!
( moaning )
HE BETTER PICK HIS FIGHTS
MORE CAREFULLY--WE WON!
METEOR WING!
EEE!
HIT THE HIGHWAY!
HA HA HA!
WE GOTCHA!
WAY TO GO, GUYS--
YOU GOT BAKEMON!
HA HA HA!
HEE HEE HEE!
Joe:
IT'S AN EARTHQUAKE!
BUT WE'RE NOT SHAKING!
UH-OH, THOSE ARE
BLACK GEARS!
LOTS OF 'EM!
( grinding and snapping sounds )
Sora:
NOW WE'RE SHAKING!
Joe:
WOW, I'M SURE GLAD
THOSE BLACK GEARS BROKE.
AND I'M GLAD BAKEMON'S GONE.
LOOK, IT'S
INFINITY MOUNTAIN.
AND THAT'S
WHERE WE'RE GOING.
YEAH.
Joe:
MAYBE OUR FRIENDS
ARE THERE, SORA.
Sora:
I HOPE SO....