Matt:
WE FINALLY FOUND T.K.,
AND JUST IN TIME, TOO.
LATER, DEVIMON
CHANNELED HIS POWER
AND BECAME ENORMOUS!
NO MATTER HOW MANY TIMES
THEY TRIED,
OUR DIGIMON COULDN'T STOP HIM.
THAT'S WHEN
THE INCREDIBLE HAPPENED.
PATAMON FINALLY DIGIVOLVED
INTO ANGEMON
AND USING ALL HIS ENERGY,
DEFEATED DEVIMON!
WITH ALL HIS STRENGTH GONE,
ANGEMON RETURNED TO
THE YOUNGEST STAGE--A DIGI-EGG.
WITH DEVIMON GONE,
FILE ISLAND BEGAN REBUILDING.
I'M JUST GLAD
WE'RE ALL BACK TOGETHER AGAIN!
♪ DI-DI-DI,
DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE INTO
DIGITS OF CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE-- ♪
♪ ( bird cry ) ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Tai:
AFTER THE DIGIMON
DEFEATED DEVIMON,
WE THOUGHT THE WORST
WAS OVER.
AND THEN...
MMM...
A MYSTERIOUS BEING
APPEARED BEFORE US.
SO YOU CHILDREN
ARE THE DIGI-DESTINED.
YOU MUST BE STRONG
TO HAVE DEFEATED DEVIMON.
WHO ARE YOU?
ARE YOU A FRIEND
OF DEVIMON'S?
FEAR NOT,
FOR I AM A FRIEND TO ALL.
AND YET,
I AM A FRIEND TO NONE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT--
THERE ARE OTHER HUMANS
BESIDES US IN THIS WORLD.
I AM HUMAN,
AND YET I AM NOT HUMAN.
THIS IS CONFUSING ME!
HMMMPH!
NO, MY NAME IS GENNAI.
I WAS UNABLE TO SEND YOU
THIS TRANSMISSION
DURING YOUR BATTLE WITH DEVIMON,
BUT NOW THE LINES ARE CLEAR
AND ONLY TEN CENTS A MINUTE.
WELL, WHO ARE YOU?
AND WHERE ARE YOU?
I AM SPEAKING TO YOU
FAR AWAY FROM FILE ISLAND,
ON THE CONTINENT OF SERVER.
TALK ABOUT LONG DISTANCE--
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN HERE?
SINCE BEFORE THE BEGINNING
AND UNTIL AFTER THE END.
ARE YOU THE ONE WHO GOT US STUCK
HERE IN THE DIGITAL WORLD?
IT WAS NOT I.
THEN WHO WAS IT?
IT WAS...
...I DON'T KNOW.
All:
AWW!
BUT MR. GENNAI, SIR...
DO YOU KNOW WHAT WE NEED TO DO
SO WE CAN ALL GET BACK HOME?
NO, I DON'T.
YOU'RE A REGULAR FOUNTAIN
OF INFORMATION, AREN'T YOU?
I'M SORRY I CAN'T HELP YOU,
BUT YOU CAN HELP ME.
WHAT?
HUH?
PLEASE COME TO SERVER
AND DEFEAT OUR ENEMIES.
AS THE DIGI-DESTINED,
I HAVE FAITH IN YOU.
THAT'S CRAZY.
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
YOUR EXACT LOCATION.
GOOD POINT--I FORGOT
YOU'RE FROM OUT OF TOWN.
LET ME CREATE A MAP FOR YOU
ON YOUR COMPUTER.
HUH?!
WHAT IF YOUR ENEMIES
ARE HUMUNGAZOID?
DO YOU THINK WE CAN BEAT
ANYTHING TOUGHER THAN DEVIMON?
NOT PRESENTLY,
BUT IF YOUR DIGIMON
CAN DIGIVOLVE ONCE MORE
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO DO IT.
SO WE CAN DIGIVOLVE
EVEN MORE?
BUT YOU'LL NEED
SOMETHING SPECIAL TO DO IT.
IF YOU HAVE
THE TAGS AND CRESTS,
YOUR DIGIMON WILL BE ABLE TO
DIGIVOLVE EVEN FURTHER.
PLEASE TELL US WHERE WE CAN FIND
THESE TAGS AND CRESTS.
THE CRESTS ARE SCATTERED ABOUT,
YOU CAN LOCATE THEM THROUGHOUT
THE CONTINENT OF SERVER.
AND THE TAGS WERE SEALED AWAY
SOMEWHERE BY DEVIMON.
OH, NO! DEVIMON!
YOU MUST COME...AAHH!!!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
( Gennai in pain: )
COME QUICKLY!
I'LL BE WAITING ON SERVER!
HE'S GONE!
Mimi:
WHAT WAS THAT?
GENNAI'S TRANSMISSION
ENDED RATHER ABRUPTLY.
AT LEAST HE WAS ABLE TO
SEND A MAP THROUGH
BEFORE HE WAS CUT OFF.
I HOPE HE'S ALL RIGHT--
WHAT'S OUR NEXT MOVE?
Tai:
I'VE GOT A FOOLPROOF PLAN.
FIRST WE'LL EAT SOMETHING,
AND AFTER THAT
I'M OPEN TO SUGGESTIONS.
( Agumon giggling: )
THAT WAS DELICIOUS!
Biyomon:
I WAS SO HUNGRY.
Tentomon:
NOW THAT MY STOMACH'S FULL,
I'M READY FOR LUNCH.
T.K.?
I WAS JUST WISHING MY DIGI-EGG
WOULD HURRY UP AND HATCH
SO IT COULD GROW UP.
DON'T SWEAT IT,
LITTLE BRO,
WHEN YOUR DIGIMON HATCHES,
IT'LL BE THE COOLEST ONE YET.
EGG-ZACTLY!
Tai:
OKAY, WE'VE STUFFED OUR FACES,
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO NEXT?
Sora:
YOU KNOW WHAT'S NEXT--
WE HAVE TO GO TO SERVER
TO SAVE GENNAI FROM HIS ENEMIES.
Izzy:
ACCORDING TO MY CALCULATIONS
OF LONGITUDE AND LATITUDE,
I'D SAY SERVER IS
QUITE SOME DISTANCE FROM HERE.
I CAN'T EVEN SWIM
ACROSS THE BATHTUB,
LET ALONE AN OCEAN,
I'LL NEVER MAKE IT.
WHY DO WE
HAVE TO GO, ANYWAY?
WHAT I MEAN IS,
DEVIMON'S GONE FROM THE ISLAND,
THE BLACK GEARS
HAVE DISAPPEARED, TOO.
WE'VE BEEN
ONCE AROUND THE ISLAND,
SO WE PRETTY MUCH KNOW
WHERE EVERYTHING IS.
WE WOULDN'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT FOOD OR WATER.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
WHY SHOULD WE BELIEVE
WHAT THIS WEIRDO GENNAI SAYS?
WHAT I MEAN IS,
HOW DO WE EVEN KNOW
THAT THIS PLACE SERVER
REALLY EXISTS?
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?!
IF WE HANG AROUND HERE,
WE'LL NEVER GET BACK HOME!
I DON' KNOW, GUYS--
DEVIMON ALMOST GOT US.
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T GO,
AT LEAST WE KNOW
WHAT WE'RE UP AGAINST OVER HERE.
AND EVEN IF WE WANTED TO GO,
WHAT MODE OF TRANSPORTATION
COULD WE UTILIZE?
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
THE FASHIONS ARE LIKE ON SERVER.
MAYBE WE SHOULD STAY HERE
A WHILE AND THINK IT THROUGH.
WHAT'S WITH YOU, MAN?
T.K.:
LET'S GO!
All:
HUH?!
T.K.?
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT DANGER
WILL BE WAITING FOR US,
BUT LET'S SEE!
I'M SURE ANGEMON
WOULD SAY THE SAME THING
IF HE WERE STILL AROUND.
SO I'M GOING!
Agumon:
WE'LL GO TOO!
IF WE HAVE THE TAGS AND CRESTS,
WE CAN DIGIVOLVE AGAIN, RIGHT?
ONCE WE TRANSFORM
INTO OUR NEW SHAPES,
WE'LL BE ABLE TO
PROTECT YOU FOR SURE!
YOU DA MON!
SORA, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
OUR CHANCES FOR SUCCESS
ARE EXTREMELY HIGH.
COME ON, MIMI,
WE'LL PROBABLY BE
THE PRETTIEST FLOWERS
ON ALL OF SERVER!
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME,
I'LL SWIM TO SERVER.
COME ON--LET'S DO IT!
LET'S GO.
COUNT ME IN.
I'LL GO--I'M CONVINCED.
I'M NOT STAYING BY MYSELF--
I'LL GO TOO!
ALL RIGHT, IT'S UNANIMOUS.
THAT'S GREAT, IT'S DECIDED--
WE'RE GOING TO SERVER!
All:
Yeah!
PEPPER BREATH!
TIMBER!!!
BLUE BLASTER!
All:
AAHH!!
AT OUR CURRENT RATE,
IT'LL TAKE US FOREVER
TO BUILD A RAFT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT--
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE IN A HURRY.
HUH?
AAH!
LEOMON!
SO I HEARD YOU WERE ALL
GOING TO SERVER.
HOW DID YOU KNOW?
OH, YOU KNOW US MONSTERS,
WE ALL LOVE TO GOSSIP.
I THOUGHT I'D SEE IF YOU
NEEDED SOME HELP WITH ANYTHING.
( giggling: )
YOU MEAN YOU'LL REALLY HELP US?
I'VE GOT SOME FRIENDS
WHO WANT TO HELP AS WELL.
HMM!
EREKIMON!
MOJAMON AND CENTARAMON, TOO!
YEAH, HI--WHAT'S UP?
MONZIMON!
HEY, LOOK--
IT'S FRIGIMON!
BRRR!
( giggling: )
MERAMON!
Leomon:
FIST OF THE BEAST KING!
RRRROAAAR!
WOW, LEOMON!
All:
WHOA!
WHOO!
( all giggling )
ALRIGHT!
IT'S HYDRODYNAMICALLY DESIGNED!
I THINK
I'M GETTING SEASICK ALREADY.
GET A GRIP, JOE,
IT'LL HAVE TO DO.
BELIEVE ME,
THAT RAFT IS STRONG ENOUGH
TO GET YOU ACROSS THE OCEAN.
THANKS, LEOMON,
WE NEVER COULD HAVE DONE IT
WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
OH--!
WHAT IS IT?
( cracking sounds )
( gasps )
HI!
DIGI-EGG--
YOU HATCHED!
POYO--
POYOMON!
HOW CUTE!
THAT'S GREAT!
YEA! YEA!
HE DID IT--YEA!
( laughing joyfully )
Tentomon:
POYOMON IS A JELLYFISH-TYPE
DIGIMON OF FEW WORDS.
BUT IF HIS FRIENDS
ARE IN TROUBLE,
HE'S READY FOR ACTION!
Leomon:
THIS IS GOODBYE.
Erekimon:
AND GOOD LUCK!
Tai:
THANKS!
Sora:
GOODBYE!
All:
GOODBYE! GOOD LUCK!
Tai:
SO WE SAILED AWAY
FROM FILE ISLAND
WHERE WE HAD SOME
REALLY COOL ADVENTURES.
WE HAD TO SURVIVE ON OUR OWN--
WE GREW UP VERY FAST.
EXCEPT JOE--
HE JUST THREW UP VERY FAST.
BUT HE CAME AROUND, TOO.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT'S WAITING
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE OCEAN,
BUT WE'LL FACE IT AS A TEAM!
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
I WONDER HOW MUCH LONGER
THIS TRIP WILL TAKE.
CHILL OUT, JOE,
WE JUST LEFT.
THE SALT AIR IS
KILLING MY SINUSES,
AND WE'VE ONLY GOT ENOUGH FOOD
FOR TWO WEEKS.
IF WE RUN OUT OF FOOD,
WE'LL CATCH SOME FISH.
ONE GOOD THING--THIS IS
BEAUTIFUL WEATHER FOR SAILING.
OH, I DON'T
FEEL SO GOOD!
I DIDN'T CALCULATE
THESE WAVES BEING SO ROUGH.
HEY, HEY--POYOMON!
WHAT?
WHOA! POYOMON, BE CAREFUL!
LOOK! TIDAL WAVE!
All:
WHOOOOAAA!!!
THAT HAD TO BE
12 FEET TALL!
18.3, TO BE EXACT.
WAS THAT ANOTHER BOAT
THAT CAUSED THAT WAVE?
THERE'S NO BOAT
THAT CAN DO THAT!
AN ISLAND!
AN ISLAND?!
SINCE WHEN DOES
AN ISLAND HAVE FINS?!
( all screaming )
( screaming )
HEADS UP!
All:
WHOOAAH!!!
Tentomon:
WHAMON IS A GIANT DIGIMON
WHO LIVES IN THE DEEP OCEANS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD.
ITS JET ARROWS
ARE UNBELIEVABLE!
Gabumon:
IT WAS MASSIVE!
Tentomon:
WHAMON CAN SOMETIMES
BE FIERCE.
BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN ONE
ACT THIS AGGRESSIVE!
All:
AAAAAHHHH!!!
( screaming in horror )
Sora:
I HOPE WE DON'T GIVE HIM
A SORE THROAT!
Izzy:
TECHNICALLY IT'S NOT THE THROAT,
IT'S THE ESOPHAGUS
THAT LEADS TO THE STOMACH.
Joe:
HE THINKS WE'RE FAST FOOD!
SO HE REALLY DID EAT US!
Sora:
SOONER OR LATER,
THIS HAS TO LEAD TO AN EXIT.
Izzy:
IT DOES, BUT YOU DON'T
WANT TO GO THERE!
THIS IS DAMAGING MY HAIR
ALL THE WAY TO THE ROOTS!
USE MY ROOTS.
YOU'RE A PLANT.
WHAT IS THAT GROSS GOOEY JUNK?
Izzy:
MAYBE THEY'RE ANTIBODIES
THAT ARE ATTACKING US
BECAUSE THEY THINK
WE'RE GERMS OR SOMETHING.
Sora:
FINALLY, WE STOPPED--
IS EVERYONE OKAY?
WHERE ARE WE?
ANATOMICALLY SPEAKING,
THIS WOULD BE THE STOMACH.
THE STOMACH--
ISN'T THAT WHERE FOOD GOES
AFTER IT'S CHEWED UP?
YEAH.
GASTRIC JUICE!
WHAT?!
IT'S THE ACID IN THE STOMACH
THAT DISSOLVES THE FOOD!
( hissing )
WE'RE MELTING!
Tai:
DON'T LET IT GET ON YOU!
Joe:
WE BETTER GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE HE GETS A MAJOR ULCER.
Sora:
LOOK UP THERE!
Tai:
IT'S A BLACK GEAR!
THAT'S WHY WHAMON
WAS ACTING SO AGGRESSIVE!
Gomamon:
JOE, DO SOMETHING TO HELP!
Joe:
WHY ME?
Palmon:
SOMEONE CAN CLIMB ON THESE!
POISON IVY!
RIGHT--I'LL DO IT!
( grunting )
( digivice beeps )
Tai:
AAAAHHHH!!
WHOA!
OKAY, I DESTROYED IT!
( whooshing sounds )
( all screaming )
Biyomon:
SORA, ARE YOU OKAY?
( Sora, weakly: )
YEAH.
SOMEHOW WE GOT OUT OF THERE.
POYOMON, TALK TO ME!
YOU'RE OKAY!
GO AWAY--NOT AGAIN!
Whamon:
SORRY ABOUT THAT--
I MUST HAVE HAD A TUMMYACHE
OR SOMETHING.
IT'S OKAY--WE ALL KNOW
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
THAT'S RIGHT--IT WAS
THE BLACK GEAR INSIDE YOU.
THOSE BLACK GEARS ARE RUDE--
I'LL BET THAT WAS THE LAST ONE.
Joe:
I BET YOU'RE WRONG!
Whamon:
THANKS, KIDS--I OWE YOU ONE.
DON'T MENTION IT, WHAMON,
IT WAS OUR PLEASURE.
BY THE WAY, DO YOU KNOW
HOW FAR IT IS TO SERVER?
YES, IT WOULD TAKE ME
FIVE DAYS--
MAKE THAT THREE AND A HALF
WITHOUT TRAFFIC.
T.K.:
GREAT--OUR RAFT'S BROKEN.
Whamon:
ARE YOU GOING TO SERVER?
Agumon:
YEAH, WE WERE TRYING TO.
I'LL TAKE YOU THERE MYSELF.
IT'S NOT EVERY DAY
YOUR LUNCH SAVES YOUR LIFE.
Sora:
REALLY?
YEA! ALRIGHT!
THIS IS GREAT.
SURE IS A WHOLE LOT FASTER
AND SMOOTHER THAN THAT RAFT!
WHICH MEANS
I WON'T GET SEASICK.
NOW IF WE ONLY KNEW
WHERE WE COULD FIND
THOSE TAGS AND THOSE CRESTS
THAT DEVIMON HID SOMEWHERE.
Whamon:
DID YOU SAY DEVIMON?
Tai:
YEAH, DO YOU KNOW HIM?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT TAGS OR CRESTS,
BUT A WHILE AGO
DEVIMON HID SOMETHING
DEEP AT THE BOTTOM OF THE OCEAN.
WHERE?
Whamon:
IT'S ON THE WAY TO SERVER--
YOU CAN ALL RIDE INSIDE ME
AND I'LL TAKE YOU THERE.
BUT NO TICKLING.
Whamon:
I'M SO OUT OF SHAPE,
I HAVE TO REST HERE FOR A WHILE.
I GOTTA DROP
A COUPLE THOUSAND POUNDS.
Tai:
THANKS, WHAMON!
Joe:
WHAT'S THAT?
Tai:
A CONVENIENCE STORE!
( rumbling and cracking )
WHAT IS IT?
Agumon:
DRIMOGEMON.
RRROOAARRRR!!
Tentomon:
DRIMOGEMON LIVES
DEEP INSIDE THE EARTH
DRILLING TUNNELS.
HE USES HIS IRON DRILL SPIN
AND CRUSHER BONE
TO WIPE OUT HIS ENEMIES.
Sora:
A BLACK GEAR!
Joe:
I KNEW THAT COULDN'T HAVE BEEN
THE LAST BLACK GEAR!
Drimogemon:
IT IS LORD DEVIMON'S WILL
THAT NO ONE SHALL PASS!
GRRRRR!!!
TAI, LEAVE THIS TO US DIGIMON--
YOU TRY TO FIND THE TAGS.
GOT IT!
YOU THINK THAT DRILL SCARES US?
THINK AGAIN!
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
GOMAMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
IKKAKUMON!!!
( roars )
DRILL SPIN!
Tai:
NOW'S OUR CHANCE!
( all screaming )
IKKAKUMON!
YOU GOT HIM DOWN, GET HIM!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
(all screaming )
I THINK IT'S TIME
I JOINED THE BATTLE!
TENTOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
KABUTERIMON!!!
AAH!!!
CRUSHER BONE!
KABUTERIMON,
AIM FOR THE BLACK GEAR!
ELECTRO-SHOCKER!
ARRRGGGHHH!!
ELECTRO-SHOCKER! ARRGGHHH!!
( explosion sound )
POYOMON! WHERE ARE YOU?!
POYOMON!
OH, POYOMON!
COME ON,
YOU CAN'T STAY IN THIS STORE!
WHAT'S IN THE BOX?
PLEASE FORGIVE ME
FOR ATTACKING YOU.
PARDON ME--
DO YOU KNOW WHERE THE TAGS ARE?
THE TAGS WOULD BE
IN THE CONVENIENCE STORE,
NEXT TO THE JERKY.
THE TAGS!
LIKE THE ONES GENNAI SHOWED US
DURING HIS TRANSMISSION!
Mimi:
HOW PRETTY!
( sighing contentedly )
REMEMBER WHAT
GENNAI TOLD US, GUYS.
THE CRESTS ARE SCATTERED OVER
THE CONTINENT OF SERVER.
AND IF WE GET
BOTH THE TAGS AND THE CRESTS,
WE'LL ALL BE ABLE TO
DIGIVOLVE ONCE AGAIN!
THEN WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
GO OUT AND FIND THE CRESTS!