Tai: MATT AND I
WERE HAVING A DISAGREEMENT
WHEN SUDDENLY AN ENTITY
BEGAN TO SPEAK THROUGH KARI.
IT SHOWED US IMAGES
WHEN WE FIRST SAW THE DIGIMON.
NEXT WE SAW PIEDMON ATTEMPTING
TO STEAL THE DIGIEGGS
OF WHAT WERE TO EVENTUALLY
BECOME OUR DIGIMON.
A YOUNG GENNAI RESCUED THE EGGS
AND TOOK THEM TO FILE ISLAND,
WHERE WE FIRST FOUND THEM.
AFTER OUR HISTORY LESSON,
KARI RETURNED TO NORMAL,
BUT MATT STILL WANTED TO LEAVE.
MIMI AND JOE SEPARATED
FROM THE GROUP.
IF THIS KEEPS UP,
THERE WON'T BE ANYONE LEFT
TO SAVE EITHER WORLD.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
GET AWAY FROM ME,
YOU PILE-OF-WOODMON!
I KNOW YOUR TRICKS.
YOU PRETEND YOU'RE TREES,
THEN ABSORB THE ENERGY
FROM UNSUSPECTING DIGIMON
AS THEY PASS BY.
THIS IS YOUR LAST WARNING.
YOU ASKED FOR IT!
HOW MANY WOODMON
CAN AN OGREMON CHUCK
IF AN OGREMON
COULD CHUCK WOODMON?
POMAWA!
[ ALL SCREAM ]
THEY SURE RUN FAST
FOR TREE STUMPS.
THIS IS GOOD.
CAN I TELL YOU SOMETHING?
WHAT?
I HOPE I WASN'T TOO SELFISH
FOR SAYING I DIDN'T WANT
TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
IN FACT, YOU WERE BRAVE.
WHAT YOU SAID WAS TRUE.
FIGHTING JUST LEADS
TO MORE FIGHTING,
AND THEN NOTHING
EVER GETS RESOLVED.
MY BROTHER JIM USED
TO SAY THE SAME THING
AFTER HE'D GET BEAT UP.
JOE?
WHAT IS IT, JOE?
IT'S NOTHING.
NEVER MIND.
DON'T KEEP THINGS
BOTTLED UP INSIDE.
IT'S NOT HEALTHY.
DON'T TELL ME
ABOUT NOT BEING HEALTHY.
I'VE BEEN NOT HEALTHY
MY WHOLE LIFE.
IF I WANT TO KEEP THINGS
BOTTLED UP, I WILL!
SOMEBODY NEEDS A TIMEOUT.
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO LEND A FRIENDLY EAR.
Joe: I KNOW YOU WERE, GOMAMON.
SORRY, BUDDY.
WHAT IS THAT THING?
IT LOOKS LIKE A METEORITE.
LOOK OUT!
IT'S COMING THIS WAY.
I CAN'T GET RID
OF YOU GUYS.
YOU'RE NOT TREES.
YOU'RE WEEDS.
IT CAN'T ALL END LIKE THIS,
NOT BEFORE I BEAT LEOMON.
WHAT IN THE WORLD?
THAT THING IS MONSTROUS!
IT'S HEADING RIGHT FOR US.
AAH!
[ CHILDREN SCREAMING ]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WAS THAT SOME SORT
OF EXPLOSION?
AN EARTHQUAKE?
A METEOR!
AND I MEAN A WHOPPER.
IT JUST CRASHED
IN THE FOREST.
Tai: TOTALLY COOL.
LET'S GO CHECK IT OUT.
I DON'T KNOW, TAI.
IT COULD BE DANGEROUS.
LET'S HEAD TO PUPPETMON'S
MANSION INSTEAD.
WE'LL SHOW YOU GUYS
EXACTLY WHERE IT IS.
HE'S ONE OF THE DARK MASTERS.
WE'LL HAVE TO FIGHT HIM
SOONER OR LATER.
YEAH, IT'S TIME
SOMEBODY CUT HIS STRINGS.
LET'S TAKE THE FIGHT TO HIM
FOR A CHANGE.
IF WE DON'T HURRY UP,
I'M AFRAID BOTH OUR WORLDS
WILL BE DESTROYED.
LET'S DO IT, TAI.
LET'S THINK THIS OVER.
PUPPETMON IS A MEGADIGIMON,
AND WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO DEFEAT HIM THAT EASILY.
IN THAT CASE, LET'S GIVE UP
AND GO WATCH CARTOONS.
ALL THOSE IN FAVOR OF GOING
TO PUPPETMON'S MANSION,
RAISE YOUR HAND AND SAY AYE.
All: AYE!
THE AYES HAVE IT.
TAI, YOU DIDN'T VOTE.
[ Thinking ] I WONDER
HOW MATT WOULD VOTE.
HE'D PROBABLY GO
THE SAFE ROUTE.
SO, TAI,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
AND WHAT ABOUT T.K.?
IT'S MY JOB TO MAKE SURE
NOTHING HAPPENS TO HIM.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
WE'RE WAITING FOR AN ANSWER.
[ Thinking ] HE CAN'T REALLY
BE THINKING ABOUT GOING.
WE'RE GOING
JUST TO TAKE A LOOK.
WE DON'T HAVE TO
START ANY TROUBLE.
All: OKAY!
T.K.: IT'S THIS WAY, GUYS.
SORA?
I'LL GO ALONG, BUT I'M STILL
NOT SURE IT'S SAFE.
I KNOW IT'S DANGEROUS,
BUT IF ANYTHING HAPPENS,
KOROMON AND I
WILL HOLD OFF PUPPETMON
WHILE YOU TAKE THE OTHERS
AND ESCAPE.
I WON'T LET ANYTHING
HAPPEN TO YOU.
YOU MEAN IT?
OF COURSE I DO.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BOYS AND GIRLS,
GET READY FOR THE COMEBACK TOUR
OF THE YEAR.
BABY, I'M BACK!
UH-HUH, YEAH!
Joe: LOOK, THERE IT IS.
THE METEOR LANDED UP
ON THAT CLIFF.
I WONDER WHERE ON EARTH
IT COULD HAVE COME FROM.
PROBABLY L.A.
HUH?
WHAT?
I SMELL SOMETHING
FROM OVER THERE.
WAIT!
Mimi: HEY, NOT SO FAST.
I MIGHT SWEAT.
Palmon: AND I KEEP TRIPPING
ON MY ROOTS.
All: HUH?
Gomamon: I THINK
SOMEONE'S HURT.
Palmon: HANG IN THERE.
WE'RE COMING.
WE'VE GOT TO
GET THESE BRANCHES
OFF OF HIM.
OGREMON! YIKES,
WE BETTER GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE HE WAKES UP.
[ GRUNTS ]
IT LOOKS LIKE HE'S HURT.
Joe: REMEMBER HIM
FROM FILE ISLAND?
HE WAS MEANER THAN A CAT
GETTING A BATH.
LET'S PRETEND LIKE
WE NEVER FOUND HIM.
HEY!
MIMI, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS CUT LOOKS BAD.
OH!
[ GROWLING ]
YOU'RE THE DIGIDESTINED.
I GUESS
YOU DON'T HAVE AMNESIA.
TRY NOT TO MOVE ANYWAY, OKAY?
[ GROANS ]
PALMON, LOOK
FOR SOME HEALING HERBS,
AND, GOMAMON,
FIND SOME WATER.
Both: RIGHT!
JOE, I WANT YOU TO --
MY FATHER IS A DOCTOR,
AND HE TAUGHT ME A LOT.
I USED TO PRACTICE
ON MY TOYS.
TOYS? OHH...
I TOLD YOU NOT TO MOVE.
OKAY.
OW, THAT STUFF BURNS!
BE CAREFUL!
DON'T YOU WANT TO
GET BETTER?
HIS ARM MIGHT BE BROKEN.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
PUT IT IN A SLING.
OOH, TOILET PAPER!
DO YOU HAVE TO NOW?
I'M USING IT AS BANDAGES.
BEFORE WE CAME BACK,
I THOUGHT OF THINGS
WE MIGHT NEED,
AND TOILET PAPER
CAME TO MY MIND.
THERE, JUST ABOUT
FINISHED HERE. WELL?
FEELS SOFT.
IT MUST BE 2-PLY.
LAY OFF THE DIGEVOLVING,
AND YOU'LL BE AS GOOD AS NEW.
OW!
JOE, I NEVER KNEW
YOU WERE SO RESOURCEFUL.
WHY ARE YOU DIGIDESTINED
BEING SO NICE TO ME,
ESPECIALLY AFTER I TRIED
TO DESTROY YOU ON FILE ISLAND?
YOU COULD HAVE LEFT ME
HERE TO ROT.
INSTEAD YOU SAVED ME. WHY?
WE WERE TAUGHT THAT
IF SOMEONE'S IN TROUBLE,
YOU ALWAYS HELP THEM OUT,
EVEN IF THEY WERE TRYING
TO PUMMEL YOU INTO OBLIVION.
GEE, I NEVER THOUGHT
OF IT THAT WAY.
I OWE YOU ONE.
DON'T MENTION IT.
THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS DO --
THEY HELP EACH OTHER OUT.
WAIT! DON'T LEAVE NOW.
I NEVER HAD ANY FRIENDS.
OH, WELL,
YOU HAVE THEM NOW.
[ CRYING ]
Palmon: I'VE NEVER SEEN
OGREMON CRY BEFORE.
DON'T TELL ME YOU NEED
MORE TOILET PAPER.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL JUST USE MY SLEEVE.
THAT'S GOT TO HURT
WITH ALL THOSE SPIKES!
HERE'S A RIDDLE --
WHAT HAS FOUR STRINGS
AND IS MADE OF WOOD?
All: PUPPETMON!
NO, A VIOLIN,
BUT THAT'S A GOOD GUESS.
I GUESS YOU GUYS
AREN'T MUSIC LOVERS.
Gomamon: IT'S YOU
WE DON'T LIKE.
DO YOU LIKE THIS?
AAH!
I CAN ALSO PLAY
A REALLY MEAN SAXOPHONE.
I'VE GOT TO DIGEVOLVE!
[ Thinking ] OH, NO!
WHAT IF TOGEMON GETS HURT
DURING THE FIGHT?
GOMAMON, DIGEVOLVE!
RIGHT!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
GOMAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
IKKAKUMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HARPOON TORPEDO!
[ GRUNTS ]
AAH!
HA HA HA!
HUH?
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
IKKAKUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
ZUDOMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
TAKE THIS! PUPPET PUMMEL!
ODIN'S HAMMER!
HA HA HA!
DON'T TELL ME
PLAYTIME'S OVER.
[ ETEMON YELLING ]
ALL RIGHT, ALREADY!
GET DIGI WITH IT.
METALETEMON'S IN THE HOUSE.
WHO'S THAT GUY?
A SUPERSTAR LIKE ME DESERVES
A LITTLE APPLAUSE, BABY.
AFTER ALL, IT'S BEEN SO LONG
SINCE WE'VE SEEN EACH OTHER.
OH, NO, IT'S ETEMON!
I USED TO BE ETEMON, KID,
BUT THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
NOW I'M METALETEMON!
WELL, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
Gomamon: WE THOUGHT
ETEMON WAS TOUGH.
METALETEMON IS A MEGADIGIMON.
AFTER HIS BANANA ATTACK,
HE'LL PEEL US OFF THE FLOOR.
JUST WHAT WE NEED --
NEW AND UNIMPROVED.
LET ME TELL YOU
HOW I BECAME ME.
[ AUDIENCE CHEERS ]
♪ NOW, HE'S LOOKING STYLED ♪
♪ WHEN ETEMON EXPIRED ♪
♪ LISTEN UP, BABY ♪
♪ I'M SURE YOU ALL REMEMBER ♪
♪ THE BATTLE I HAD
WITH METALGREYMON ♪
♪ I TELL YOU, HE'S ONE
TOUGH DINOSAUR, HONEY ♪
♪ AFTER THAT, I WAS SWALLOWED UP
BY A BLACK HOLE ♪
♪ I THINK
I GAVE IT INDIGESTION ♪
♪ MY DIGITAL INFORMATION
WAS SCATTERED ♪
♪ THROUGHOUT THE UNIVERSE ♪
♪ I PULLED MYSELF TOGETHER ♪
♪ AND CHILLED OUT FOR A WHILE
IN DIGIMON LIMBO ♪
♪ MY INFORMATION WAS CHOPPED,
MIXED, WHIPPED, AND PURéED ♪
♪ I FELT LIKE
A 4-SPEED BLENDER, HONEY ♪
♪ BUT I REFUSED TO RETURN
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ UNTIL I WAS BIGGER, BETTER ♪
♪ AND HAD A FULL HEAD
OF BEAUTIFUL METAL HAIR ♪
♪ NOW I'M BACK
TO GET MY REVENGE ON YOU ♪
♪ DIGIDESTINED ♪
♪ I'VE GOT THE LOWDOWN,
DIRTY, REVENGEFUL -- OW! ♪
♪ I'M TALKING
BIG-TIME DIGIDESTINED RUDE ♪
ENOUGH!
I JUST GOT STARTED THERE,
YOU OVERSIZED FOOTSTOOL.
WHO ARE YOU CALLING
OVERSIZED?
WATCH YOUR STEP!
BANANA SLIP!
TOO MUCH OF A WAXY BUILDUP?
PUPPET PUMMEL!
OW! I'LL USE YOU
AS A TOOTHPICK!
METAL POW!
AAH!
YOU FIGHT DIRTY!
I'M NOT DIRTY. I JUST GOT
DETAILED AT THE CAR WASH.
NOW'S OUR CHANCE
TO ESCAPE!
[ ALL PANTING ]
NYAH-NYAH-NYAH!
OH! AAH!
HA HA HA HA!
Tai: SO THAT'S
PUPPETMON'S MANSION, HUH?
THERE ARE TWO GUARDS.
SEE WHO THEY ARE.
ANALYZING.
ONE OF THEM IS FLORIMON.
SHE'S A PLANT-TYPE DIGIMON
WHO DIGEVOLVES
LIKE A REPTILE.
HER ATTACK
IS RAIN OF POLLEN.
THE OTHER GUARD IS...
DARIMON.
IT LOOKS LIKE
A BIRD-TYPE DIGIMON,
°BUT IT'S GOT A PLANT
GROWING OUT OF ITS BACK.
SO THEY'RE NOT ULTIMATE
DIGIMON, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
WE SHOULD BE CAREFUL.
THEY COULD BE DANGEROUS.
SHALL WE GO?
THERE MIGHT BE
MORE GUARDS INSIDE.
I'LL GO INSIDE AND MAKE SURE
THE COAST IS CLEAR. WAIT HERE.
I THINK PATAMON AND I
SHOULD GO WITH YOU.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES WHO KNOW
WHERE EVERYTHING IS INSIDE.
RIGHT.
SORRY.
IT MIGHT BE DANGEROUS.
TAI, DON'T TREAT ME
LIKE A LITTLE KID.
THAT'S NOT IT.
Kari: WHAT IF WE GO
TOGETHER AS A TEAM?
THERE'S NOTHING TO BE
AFRAID OF IF WE GO TOGETHER.
WHAT DO WE DO?
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
WE'RE GOING. FOLLOW ME!
OH! OW! OW! OW!
HEY! CUT IT OUT!
HA HA HA HA!
AAH! HA HA HA!
HEY, QUIT IT!
I HATE TICKLING! COME ON!
NOW I CAN TAKE CARE
OF THOSE KIDS.
THEY'RE GONE!
IT'S YOUR FAULT, YOU PIECE
OF ROTTED DRIFTWOOD!
YOU RECYCLED TIN CAN!
BIG DUMB KNOTHOLE!
AAH!
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HOME. YOU'RE LOUSY
AT NAME-CALLING.
I'M METAL AND YOU'RE WOOD.
WHATEVER YOU SAY BOUNCES
OFF ME AND SPLITS YOU IN HALF.
WHO NEEDS HIM, ANYWAY?
I CAN FIND THOSE
DIGIDESTINED MYSELF.
AFTER ALL, I AM
THE ULTIMATE METAL DETECTOR.
LET'S GO!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
KOROMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
AGUMON!
SUPER SHOCKER!
I'LL GET HIM!
HYPERBREATH!
WHOA!
IF YOU WANTED FRIED CHICKEN,
YOU COULD HAVE ASKED.
WE THOUGHT YOU WERE
PROTECTING
PUPPETMON'S MANSION.
OH, SO YOU BARBECUE ME.
WE'RE NOT PROTECTING
ANYTHING.
THEN WHAT ARE
YOU GUYS DOING?
Darimon: WELL, WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE PUPPETMON'S PLAYMATES --
SOMEONE TO CHASE AROUND
AND ATTACK WHEN HE GETS BORED.
BUT LET ME FILL YOU IN --
PUPPETMON
IS AN OBNOXIOUS JERK,
AND NONE OF US
CAN STAND HIM.
NOW I REMEMBER.
PUPPETMON DOESN'T
HAVE ANY FRIENDS,
EVEN THOUGH
HE THINKS HE DOES.
WOW. WHAT COULD BE WORSE
THAN HAVING A LIFE
WITHOUT A SINGLE FRIEND?
A LITTER BOX LINED
WITH FLY PAPER.
[ LAUGHS ]
SO IS PUPPETMON
INSIDE THE HOUSE RIGHT NOW?
I THINK HE'S OUT BEING
FUMIGATED FOR TERMITES.
SO WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
WELL, NOW'S A GOOD CHANCE
TO TAKE A LOOK
INSIDE THE MANSION.
WILL YOU SHOW US AROUND?
SURE. I USED TO BE
A TOUR GUIDE
AT DIGIMON STUDIOS.
OH, NO VIDEO CAMERAS,
FLASH PHOTOGRAPHY, FOOD,
OR DRINK ARE ALLOWED
DURING THE TOUR.
All: GREAT! LET'S GO!
THE MAIN STRUCTURE
WAS BUILT
BEFORE
THE DIGITAL REVOLUTION.
HOW HARD COULD IT BE
TO FIND A BUNCH OF KIDS?
[ METALETEMON YELLS ]
SO, DOES IT STILL HURT?
ACTUALLY, NO, NOT REALLY.
I NEED TO KNOW HOW I CAN
EVER THANK YOU ALL.
FORGET ABOUT IT.
YOU DON'T NEED TO THANK US.
NO, I HAVE TO.
IT'S AN ANCIENT TRADITION
TO REPAY ALL ACTS
OF KINDNESS.
IT'S PART
OF MY SACRED MORAL CODE
AS AN OGREMON.
WHAT ARE YOU,
A MEMBER OF KING ARTHUR'S
COURT OR SOMETHING?
OH, THAT'S SO ROMANTIC.
I'M SORRY. I'LL TRY
TO BE MEANER NEXT TIME.
YEAH, YOU'LL RUIN
YOUR REPUTATION.
[ LAUGHING ]
[ ALL SCREAM ]
Tai: WHAT WAS THAT?
IT'S A JACK-IN-THE-BOX
WITH A SERIOUS ATTITUDE.
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN
TO BE LEADING US
INTO SOME SORT OF A TRAP,
WOULD YOU?
WHY, OF COURSE NOT.
I WOULD NEVER TRY ANYTHING
AS DECEITFUL AS PUPPETMON,
CROSS MY WINGS
AND HOPE TO FLY -- HONEST.
I BELIEVE HIM, TAI.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
OH, BOY!
IT'S A TOY!
OH, NO! MAKE SURE
YOU DON'T TOUCH IT!
UH-OH.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WATCH OUT! GET DOWN!
IT WAS
A HEAT-ACTIVATED BOMB.
THAT'S WHY I SAID
DON'T TOUCH ANYTHING.
Both: SORRY.
OGREMON, CAN I ASK YOU
A PERSONAL QUESTION?
YES, IT'S TRUE,
I DON'T FLOSS.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
I WAS GOING TO ASK.
WHY DO YOU FIGHT
WITH LEOMON?
DO YOU HATE HIM?
NO, NO, IT'S NOT
A QUESTION OF HATE.
IT'S OUR DESTINY
TO FIGHT EACH OTHER.
HE AND I WILL BE RIVALS
FOR ALL ETERNITY.
WELL, IF THAT'S
YOUR ONLY PURPOSE IN LIFE,
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN
IF YOU ACTUALLY WON?
I NEVER REALLY
THOUGHT ABOUT IT BEFORE.
MAYBE I'LL TAKE A VACATION.
A CRUISE IS NICE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
AND AFTER THAT?
WELL, IF THE FIGHT'S OVER,
YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE A RIVAL ANYMORE.
HE AND I ARE LIKE
TWO OLD WARRIORS,
FIGHTING A WAR THAT HAD
NO BEGINNING AND NO END.
WHY, THE ONLY REASON
I EXIST AT ALL
IS TO DEFEAT LEOMON,
AND IF HE WERE GONE --
WELL, I'M SO CONFUSED.
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE MORE
OF A PURPOSE IN LIFE.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
YOU CAN'T POSSIBLY UNDERSTAND.
THIS RIVALRY IS AS OLD
AS TIME ITSELF.
I DON'T CARE WHAT HAPPENS.
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT
AFTER I'VE DEFEATED LEOMON.
YOU'RE GETTING
WAY TOO EXCITED.
I BETTER TAKE
YOUR BLOOD PRESSURE.
[ METALETEMON YELLS ]
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT CAME FROM OUT HERE.
I FOUND YOU.
RUN!
HMM...WHO SHOULD I
PLAY WITH NEXT?
PUPPETMON'S COMING BACK.
ARE YOU READY?
IT WOULD HELP
IF I HAD SOME IDEA
OF HOW THIS WORKED.
YOU DO IT.
WHAT? THAT'S AGAINST EVERY
PRINCIPLE I STAND FOR.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL DO IT,
BUT DON'T TELL PUPPETMON.
IT'LL BE OUR SECRET. SHH.
WE KNOW.
YEAH, YEAH.
OKAY, I'VE GOT HIM
IN MY SIGHTS.
READY, AIM, FIRE!
I CAN SEE HIM COMING!
TAKE THIS, PUPPETMON!
Puppetmon: AAH!
WHO'S SHOOTING AT ME?
I KNOW WHO IT IS.
IT'S THE DIGIDESTINED.
HEY, THAT'S NOT FAIR.
YOU'RE USING MY TOY.
[ SCREAMING ]
YOU CAN'T HIDE FROM ME.
I'M THE KING OF SWING.
[ YELLING ]
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
[ GROWLING ]
WHAT IS THAT?
FRIEND OR FOE?
[ LAUGHS ]
WHO IS THIS NEW CREATURE?
COULD HE BE
ORGEMON'S ARCHRIVAL?
AND WILL PUPPETMON ESCAPE
DARIMON'S CANNON BLAST
TO TAKE HIS REVENGE
ON THE DIGIDESTINED?
TUNE IN FOR THE NEXT EPISODE
OF "DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS."