Matt: T.K. AND I
WERE LOOKING FOR PATAMON
WHEN WE RAN INTO
MYOTISMON'S HENCHMEN --
PUMPKINMON AND GOTSUMON.
THEY WERE SUPPOSED TO BE
SEARCHING FOR THE EIGHTH CHILD,
BUT ALL THEY WANTED TO DO
IS CAUSE TROUBLE.
MYOTISMON SHOWED UP
AND DIDN'T LIKE THEIR ATTITUDE.
HE BLASTED THEM BACK
TO THE DIGIWORLD.
WEREGARURUMON PUT UP A FIGHT,
BUT IT WASN'T ENOUGH.
LUCKILY, PATAMON FOUND US
AND DIGEVOLVED INTO ANGEMON.
BAT-FOR-BRAINS TOOK OFF,
BUT I'M SURE HE'LL RETURN,
AND HE WON'T BE HAPPY.
OF COURSE, HE'S NEVER HAPPY.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Tai: HEY, MOM, I'M HOME!
TAI, YOU'RE LATE.
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
I'LL GET IT.
HELLO, KAMIYA RESIDENCE.
YEAH, JOE.
SO, DID YOU FIND THE EIGHTH
DIGIDESTINED KID YET?
No. I didn't have any luck.
There weren't
any other students
who moved
from Highton View Terrace.
BUT THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
THERE MUST BE SOMEONE ELSE.
Well, whoever it is, they
weren't in my address book.
Check your own book before
you start yelling at me.
WHAT DID I DO
WITH MY BOOK, ANYWAY?
You still haven't found it?
Oh, great.
It's only the future
of the world depending on you.
I'LL FIND IT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M TRYING TO FIND
MY ADDRESS BOOK.
MIKO, TAI'S ROOM IS MESSIER
THAN YOUR LITTER BOX.
[ MEOWS ]
[ Thinking ]
IF KARI REALLY IS
THE EIGHTH DIGIDESTINED CHILD,
THEN I HAVE TO DESTROY HER.
BUT EVERY TIME I SEE HER,
I GET THIS STRANGE SENSATION.
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY I WASN'T ABLE TO ATTACK HER
WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE.
[ MEOWS ]
HI.
[ GASPS ]
COME HERE.
AAH!
ARE YOU GOING ALREADY?
WHAT HAPPENED?
I COULD HAVE STOPPED
THE DIGIDESTINED
ONCE AND FOR ALL,
BUT SOMETHING
WAS PULLING ME AWAY.
LOOK AT THAT PET CAT
OVER THERE.
SHE GETS FED GOURMET FOOD
OUT OF A CAN.
SHE GETS TO CHASE A SOCK.
TALK ABOUT A PURR-FECT LIFE.
NOBODY WAS NICE TO ME
WHEN I WAS GROWING UP.
NOBODY WAS NICE, PERIOD.
[ GASPS ]
BACK WHEN I WAS SALAMON,
I WAS A SLAVE
TO THE EVIL MYOTISMON.
Myotismon: EVERY TIME
YOU LOOK AT ME
WITH THOSE EYES,
I'LL HAVE TO HURT YOU.
I COULDN'T UNDERSTAND IT.
HE JUST DIDN'T LIKE MY EYES.
THIS IS ONE OF THE SCARS
THAT MYOTISMON GAVE ME
JUST BECAUSE I HAVE THESE EYES.
I WISH I COULD REMEMBER
WHERE I WAS BORN.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT I DID
BEFORE I MET MYOTISMON.
MY PAST IS A BLUR.
THINKING ABOUT
THE GOOD OLD DAYS?
I'M NOT GOING
TO TELL YOU AGAIN.
DON'T READ MY THOUGHTS
WITHOUT MY PERMISSION.
I'M SORRY, GATOMON.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
AND SHOULDN'T YOU
BE OUT LOOKING
FOR THE EIGHTH
DIGIDESTINED HUMAN?
YES.
I'LL GET RIGHT ON IT.
HA HA HA.
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
STILL NO REACTION
FROM THE CREST.
IT'S REACTING!
I WONDER WHAT'S CAUSING IT.
[ CAWING ]
THE DIGIVICE! THUNDER BALL!
Demidevimon: HEY, WIZARDMON,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OVER THERE?
UH, NOTHING.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE YOU CAME
OUT HERE TO DO NOTHING.
TELL ME WHAT YOU FOUND.
ALL RIGHT,
BUT IF I SHOW YOU,
YOU HAVE TO PROMISE
NOT TO TELL ANYONE.
COME ON, SHOW ME!
IT'S A BOTTLE
OF GREEN CHILI SAUCE.
IT'S GREAT ON TACOS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING EATING
WHEN THERE'S WORK TO BE DONE?
YOU SHOULD BE LOOKING FOR
THE EIGHTH DIGIDESTINED CHILD
LIKE THE OTHERS.
PLEASE DON'T TELL
LORD MYOTISMON.
WHY DON'T YOU GET RID
OF THIS FOR ME?
ALL RIGHT.
I HOPE THE ALL-NIGHT
DRIVE-THRU IS STILL OPEN.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M HANDING
THIS OVER TO DEMIDEVIMON.
HE'LL TAKE ALL THE CREDIT
FOR HIMSELF.
BUT WAIT,
IF THE DIGIVICE IS HERE,
WHERE IS THE EIGHTH CHILD?
Man: BOTH HORSES WERE REPORTED
TO BE IN STABLE CONDITION.
NOW BACK TO OUR TOP STORY.
SEVERAL MORE STRANGE MONSTERS
HAVE BEEN SIGHTED TODAY
IN AND AROUND THE TOKYO AREA.
THERE HAVE BEEN MORE REPORTS
OF YOUNG GIRLS
BEING STRUCK DOWN BY WHAT
DOCTORS CALL "SUDDEN ANEMIA."
INVESTIGATORS SAY THESE
INCIDENTS MAY BE RELATED.
NOW ON TO THE WEATHER.
SUDDEN ANEMIA?
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
Tai: I'LL GET IT.
HELLO.
Tai?
MATT, DID YOU SEE
THE NEWS?
I didn't have to
because I was there.
We just got back
from the city.
SO THAT REPORT
ON TELEVISION WAS...
Right. It was Myotismon,
and was he on the war path.
He even got rid of two
of his own flunkies.
We don't know how much
time we've got left.
We've got to hurry up
and find the eighth child.
MYOTISMON WILL MANGLE HIM
IF HE FINDS HIM BEFORE WE DO.
WIZARDMON, WHAT IS IT NOW?
GO AWAY BEFORE I USE YOU
AS MY SCRATCHING POST.
SORRY TO DISTURB YOU AGAIN,
BUT --
BUT WHAT?
THE DIGIVICE!
WHERE DID YOU GET IT?
I FOUND IT IN A CROW'S NEST
IN THE ARAKAY WOODS.
THEN THE EIGHTH DIGIDESTINED
MUST BE SOMEWHERE NEAR THERE.
NO, THE EIGHTH CHILD IS --
TELL ME RIGHT NOW!
WELL, YOU SEE, GATOMON --
WHAT?
I WONDER IF THE LOCATION
OF THE CHILD
ISN'T SOMEWHERE
INSIDE YOUR OWN HEART.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I BELIEVE THAT LONG AGO
YOU BURIED AWAY
AN IMPORTANT PART
OF YOURSELF,
AND SOMEWHERE DEEP INSIDE
YOUR HEART
LIES THE KEY
TO THE IDENTITY
OF THE EIGHTH
DIGIDESTINED CHILD.
TRY TO REMEMBER.
WHAT'S HOLDING YOU BACK?
COULD IT BE YOU'RE AFRAID
OF WHAT YOU MIGHT FIND?
YOU CAN GET YOUR LOST
MEMORIES BACK, GATOMON.
YOU CAN REMEMBER YOUR PAST
WITHOUT FEAR.
END YOUR LONG NIGHTMARE
AND TRY TO REMEMBER.
LEAVE ME ALONE! WHO SENT
YOU HERE -- MYOTISMON?
MYOTISMON HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS.
I FIGHT BY YOUR SIDE,
NOT HIS.
I TELL YOU THESE THINGS NOW
BECAUSE YOU ARE MY FRIEND.
BEFORE I MET YOU,
I WAS ALWAYS ALONE.
I WAS CONSTANTLY TRAVELING,
NEVER STOPPING
TO MAKE ANY FRIENDS.
THEN ONE DAY I FELL
FROM THE SKY AND CRASHED,
BUT NO ONE STOPPED
TO HELP ME,
AND I THOUGHT
I WAS A GONER
UNTIL YOU CAME.
Gatomon: HERE, DRINK THIS.
LOOKS LIKE HE PASSED OUT.
AH, YOU'RE AWAKE.
HUH? DID YOU SAVE ME?
I DIDN'T DO THAT MUCH.
I JUST COULDN'T LEAVE YOU
LYING THERE.
WELL, THANKS.
I GUESS I'LL BE GOING NOW.
YOU'RE NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO GO.
I KNOW YOU HELPED ME, BUT I
DON'T HAVE ANYTHING FOR YOU.
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING,
BUT YOU MUST BE VERY LONELY
TO SAY THAT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHEN YOU'VE BEEN ALONE
FOR A LONG TIME,
YOUR HEART BECOMES VERY HARD.
IT HAPPENS TO EVERYONE,
YOU KNOW, EVEN ME.
I DON'T REMEMBER
ANY OF THAT.
WELL, THAT'S HOW IT HAPPENED.
I THOUGHT YOU SAVED ME
BECAUSE YOU WANTED SOMETHING.
I COULDN'T UNDERSTAND
THE CONCEPT OF COMPASSION
BECAUSE LONELINESS
HAD HARDENED MY HEART,
BUT YOU TAUGHT ME ALL CREATURES
HAVE GOOD INSIDE OF THEM.
THAT'S WHEN YOU TOLD ME
YOUR SECRET.
MY WHOLE LIFE, I JUST KEEP
WAITING AND SEARCHING,
BUT I NEVER FIND HER.
FIND WHO?
WHO ARE YOU WAITING
AND SEARCHING FOR?
I CAN'T REMEMBER.
IT WAS TOO LONG AGO.
ALL I KNOW IS
I'M WAITING FOR SOMEONE.
WAITING -- ME?
THAT'S WHAT YOU TOLD ME.
WHY CAN'T I REMEMBER
WHO I WAS WAITING FOR?
WHO COULD IT POSSIBLY BE?
[ CAT MEOWS ]
Kari: MIKO!
YOU CAN'T COME OUT HERE
AT THIS HOUR.
GO BACK INSIDE.
GOOD KITTY.
HMM.
I THINK YOUR SEARCH
IS FINALLY OVER.
HUH?
[ Gasps ]
WHO ARE YOU?
WIZARDMON.
HOW ARE YOU ABLE
TO FLY?
OH, WELL, I, UH...
OH, IT'S YOU.
HELLO AGAIN.
YOU'RE AGUMON'S FRIEND,
AREN'T YOU?
HOW COME YOU RAN AWAY
LAST TIME I SAW YOU?
WHAT'S THAT THING?
CAN I SEE IT?
[ GASPS ]
WIZARDMON, IS THIS GIRL
THE EIGHTH DIGIDESTINED?
YES.
WELL, THEN WHO
IS HER DIGIMON?
I THINK YOU KNOW.
YOU WERE WAITING FOR SOMEONE.
TRY TO REMEMBER.
HOLD ON. MY MEMORY
IS STARTING TO COME BACK.
YES, I WAS DEFINITELY
WAITING FOR SOMEONE.
EVER SINCE I WAS NYAROMON,
I WAS SO LONELY.
EVERY DAY I JUST KEPT
WAITING AND WAITING.
THE SEASONS CHANGED
AND THE YEARS ROLLED BY,
AND STILL I KEPT WAITING,
BUT NO ONE EVER CAME.
THEN WHEN I BECAME SALAMON,
I STARTED SEARCHING.
I WENT ON A JOURNEY,
BUT WHAT I FINALLY FOUND
WAS NOT THE SOMEONE
I HAD BEEN WAITING FOR.
[ GASPS ]
[ BATS SCREECHING ]
INSTEAD, I FOUND EVIL
AND DARKNESS --
MYOTISMON.
THEN THOSE DAYS OF TORTURE
AND DESPAIR BEGAN,
AND I STARTED TO FORGET
THAT I WAS WAITING
FOR SOMEONE,
SEARCHING FOR SOMEONE.
Kari: WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT DOES ANY OF THIS
HAVE TO DO WITH ME?
SOMEONE'S OUT THERE
TALKING TO KARI.
HUH?
KARI, GET AWAY!
WHAT'S THE MATTER, TAI?
WHAT DO YOU DIGIMON WANT?
Wizardmon: LISTEN TO WHAT
I HAVE TO SAY.
KARI, YOU GET OVER HERE.
THOSE TWO ARE EVIL DIGIMON.
NO, THEY'RE NOT EVIL.
GATOMON HAS BEEN SEARCHING
FOR ME --
FOR ME AND THE EIGHTH
DIGIDESTINED CHILD.
WATCH OUT!
KARI, ARE YOU OKAY?
OH, NO! GATOMON!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M FINE.
THIS IS NOTHING COMPARED
TO WHAT I'VE BEEN THROUGH.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
GATOMON SAVED KARI.
NOW THAT YOU REMEMBER,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
YES, I WAS WAITING
FOR THE DIGIDESTINED HUMAN
I BELONGED WITH.
THAT'S YOU, KARI. YOU'RE
THE EIGHTH DIGIDESTINED.
YOU WERE WAITING
JUST FOR ME?
I'VE BEEN SEARCHING
FOREVER AND EVER FOR YOU.
YOU COULD HAVE JUST CALLED.
TAI, GATOMON'S MY DIGIMON.
NOW I'VE GOT ONE, TOO.
DON'T BE SILLY.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
IT MAKES PERFECT SENSE,
CONSIDERING SHE'S
THE EIGHTH DIGIDESTINED.
AND I'M HER DIGIMON.
I'LL ALWAYS PROTECT HER.
THEN WHY ARE YOU A PART
OF MYOTISMON'S ARMY,
AND WHO IS THIS GUY?
HE'S CALLED WIZARDMON.
HE PUT HIMSELF
IN GREAT DANGER
TO BRING ME THIS DIGIVICE.
HOW DO I KNOW
IF I CAN TRUST HIM OR NOT?
WHETHER YOU TRUST ME OR NOT,
I'M GOING TO FOLLOW GATOMON
AS LONG AS SHE NEEDS ME.
HERE, YOU TAKE THE DEVICE.
WHY GIVE IT TO TAI?
IT BELONGS TO KARI.
SHE CAN'T BE SEEN WITH IT.
IF MYOTISMON FINDS OUT
SHE'S THE EIGHTH CHILD
AND GATOMON IS HER DIGIMON,
THEN HE'LL DESTROY GATOMON,
AND HE WON'T REST
UNTIL HE FINDS KARI.
IF YOU HAVE THE DIGIVICE,
THEIR SECRET WILL BE SAFE.
YOU BETTER NOT BE
DOUBLE-CROSSING US.
WHAT'S NEXT?
YOUR SISTER NEEDS
HER CREST -- THE REAL ONE.
THE REAL ONE?
THIS CREST IS JUST A COPY
THAT WAS CREATED
TO FIND THE DIGIVICE.
MYOTISMON IS THE ONLY ONE
WITH ACCESS TO THE REAL CREST.
WE'VE GOT TO GET IT BACK.
Wizardmon:
LEAVE EVERYTHING TO US.
WAIT. WHERE'S
MYOTISMON'S HIDEOUT?
WE'LL COME WITH YOU.
NO, IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
Kari: BE CAREFUL, GATOMON.
CAN WE TRUST THEM?
WE HAVE TO.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
MYOTISMON HAS TO BE KEEPING
KARI'S CREST
SOMEWHERE IN THE HIDEOUT.
I THINK WE HAVE TO SEARCH
HIS ROOM.
Bakemon: STOP.
MYOTISMON IS FEEDING
UPON THE NIGHT.
HE SAID NO ONE MAY ENTER
UNTIL HE RETURNS AT DAWN.
AH, FORGET ABOUT IT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT --
THUNDER BALL!
AAH!
I CAN'T REMEMBER A THING.
WHAT WERE WE TALKING ABOUT?
WE'RE RELIEVING YOU
OF GUARD DUTY.
GO HOME
AND GET SOME SLEEP.
THAT'S RIGHT. SEE YA.
HOLD IT. DON'T FORGET
TO LEAVE US THE KEY.
OH, HERE.
THANK YOU.
Bakemon: WHAT A NICE GUY.
LET'S GO.
HURRY UP.
LET'S FIND THE CREST
AND CRUISE ON OUT.
THIS PLACE GIVES ME
THE CREEPS.
RELAX.
WE'VE GOT PLENTY OF TIME
BEFORE THE SUN COMES UP.
MYOTISMON WON'T BE BACK
FOR HOURS.
MAYBE HE KEEPS IT
IN THE COFFIN.
GOT IT!
GREAT. NOW LET'S JUST
GET OUT OF HERE.
[ BATS SCREECHING ]
UH-OH.
Myotismon: WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN HERE?
UH, NOTHING.
MAYBE I CAN ASSIST YOU.
ANOTHER COPY.
DO YOU THINK I'D LEAVE
THE ORIGINAL LYING AROUND
FOR THIEVES LIKE YOU?
[ GRUNTS ]
AAH!
WIZARDMON!
I'M ALL RIGHT.
THOSE EYES...
I KNEW YOU'D TURN AGAINST ME,
AND THAT'S WHY
I HAD TO TEACH YOU
BY PUNISHING YOU.
I WOULD'VE HURT YOU MORE,
BUT YOU BECAME A GOOD SERVANT.
I PROMISE YOU I WILL NOT BE
SO EASY ON YOU THIS TIME.
AND YOU THINK YOUR BETRAYAL
WILL GO UNPUNISHED, WIZARDMON?
HOW COULD I BETRAY YOU
WHEN I WAS NEVER
ON YOUR SIDE TO BEGIN WITH?
YOU LITTLE FOOL!
GRISLY WING!
[ BATS SCREECHING ]
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
WE REALLY HAVE
TO STAY TOGETHER.
HA HA HA!
THOSE WHO PLAY TOGETHER
LOSE TOGETHER.
I'M NOT AFRAID.
YOU SOON WILL BE,
YOU PATHETIC LITTLE TRAITOR.
MAGICAL GAME!
[ GRUNTS ]
LOOK THERE --
UP IN THE SKY!
WIZARDMON AND GATOMON
ARE IN A FIGHT!
Kari: OH, NO, I HOPE
THEY'RE NOT BEING HURT.
WHOA! LET'S GO.
RIGHT.
WAIT UP.
I WANT TO GO, TOO.
I CAN'T RISK YOU
GETTING HURT. WAIT HERE.
OH...
WELL, I HOPE YOU REALIZE
THERE'S NO SAFE PLACE TO HIDE
DURING THIS LIGHTNING STORM.
HA!
[ GATOMON HISSES ]
AAH!
MAGICAL GAME!
CRIMSON LIGHTNING!
I'LL DO AWAY
WITH YOU FIRST, WIZARDMON!
WHY DON'T YOU PICK
ON SOMEBODY 1/10 YOUR SIZE?
THERE ARE THOSE EYES AGAIN,
AND THIS TIME,
NOT ONLY ARE THEY FILLED
WITH REBELLION,
BUT I CAN ALSO SEE HOPE --
THAT ONE DAY YOUR DREAMS
WILL COME TRUE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I BELIEVE IN MY DREAMS.
JUST WHAT HAVE YOU
REALLY ACHIEVED?
YOU BELIEVE
IN YOUR WORTHLESS FRIENDS,
AND YOU BELIEVE YOUR DREAMS
CAN COME TRUE.
DREAMS DO NOT EXIST
FOR THE STUPID.
IF YOU BELIEVE IN YOURSELF,
THEN DREAMS ARE REAL,
AND TO MAKE MY DREAMS
COME TRUE,
I ONLY HAVE TO DO
ONE THING -- DEFEAT YOU!
WHAT?
MY DREAM IS FOR ME TO RETURN
TO MY TRUE IDENTITY,
THE ONE I HAD
BEFORE I MET YOU.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
TRUE IDENTITY?
COULD IT BE THAT --
ARE YOU THE EIGHTH DIGIMON?
[ SCREECHES ]
THIS CHANGES EVERYTHING.
BEFORE I CRUSH YOU,
I'LL GIVE YOU THE PLEASURE
OF WATCHING ME DESTROY
YOUR WIZARD FRIEND FIRST.
GRISLY WING!
HANG ON!
[ GRUNTING ]
AAH!
NO, NOT THAT!
OH, NO!
[ MYOTISMON
LAUGHING EVILLY ]
WE'VE COME TO HELP YOU,
GATOMON!
TAI!
QUICK,
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
NOVA BLAST!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHEN WILL YOU DIGIDESTINED
EVER LEARN?
CRIMSON LIGHTNING!
[ GRUNTS ]
GREYMON, DIGEVOLVE!
GREYMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
METALGREYMON!
[ ROARS ]
GO GET HIM,
METALGREYMON!
MEGA CLAW!
[ GRUNTS ]
GIGA BLASTER!
CRIMSON LIGHTNING!
YOU IMPUDENT FOOL,
DID YOU REALLY THINK
YOU COULD BEAT ME
WITH THOSE PATHETIC
LITTLE TOYS OF YOURS?
Tai: AGUMON!
OH, I WONDER WHAT'S
TAKING THEM SO LONG.
COME BACK, GATOMON.
I COULDN'T STAND IT
IF ANYTHING HAPPENED TO YOU,
BUT I'M SURE TAI AND AGUMON
WILL TAKE GOOD CARE OF YOU.
Tai: NICE TRY, BUDDY.
IF THE DIGIDESTINED
ARE COMING TO DEFEND GATOMON,
THEN THEY REALLY MUST THINK
SHE IS THE EIGHTH DIGIMON.
HEY, WHAT THEY THINK
IS NO BUSINESS OF YOURS.
GO BLOW SMOKE
SOMEWHERE ELSE!
YOU WILL PAY
FOR YOUR IMPUDENCE.
JUST WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
AAH!
[ Laughing evilly ] I HOPE
YOU LIKE FISHING, GATOMON,
BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING
TO BE THE PERFECT BAIT
TO LURE OUT THE EIGHTH
DIGIDESTINED CHILD.
I DON'T NEED THE CREST TO FIND
THAT COWARDLY PUNY HUMAN.
THAT'S NOT FAIR, MYOTISMON!
I DON'T PLAY FAIR.
STOP!
GATOMON!
Gatomon: TAI, HELP ME!
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
WILL TAI RESCUE GATOMON
BEFORE MYOTISMON FINDS KARI?
TUNE IN TO THE NEXT
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS."