Joe: TO GET ACROSS TOWN,
WE TOOK THE SUBWAY.
YOKOMON GOT MAD AT A BABY,
AND NEARLY GAVE US AWAY.
THE OTHER KIDS BOUGHT
FOOD WITH OUR TRAVELING MONEY.
WE HAD TO FIND A RIDE.
LUCKILY, SORA'S COUSIN
CAME BY AND PICKED US UP.
HE TURNED OUT
TO BE A REAL JERK.
HE KNOCKED IZZY OFF,
AND TENTOMON HAD TO SAVE HIM.
THEN GESOMON APPEARED AND
IKAKKUMON HAD TO TAKE HIM OUT.
TO THINK,
THERE ARE PEOPLE
WHO DO THIS COMMUTE
EVERY DAY.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
DEFEATED!
YOU SAY THOSE LITTLE PUNKS
BEAT MAMMOTHMON AND GESOMON?
RIGHT! GATOMON REALLY
BUNGLED IT
WHEN SHE HOOKED UP
WITH THOSE NINCOMPOOPS.
I GUESS SHE'S NO BETTER
THAN THE REST OF US.
HA HA.
THAT'S FUNNY?
OF COURSE NOT, BOSS!
THEN KNOCK OFF
THE CHATTER
AND FIND THE EIGHTH CHILD
BEFORE I LOSE MY PATIENCE!
AYE-AYE!
MYOTISMON RULES!
YOU'LL SEE!
HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA!
Koromon: GEE, TAI,
I SURE HOPE
THAT YOUR SISTER KARI
IS OVER HER NASTY COLD.
ME, TOO.
IT'S REALLY WEIRD.
LAST TIME
WE WERE HERE,
SHE REMEMBERED WHAT
HAD HAPPENED FOUR YEARS AGO.
OH, WOW! DO YOU THINK
IT'S POSSIBLE
THAT KARI'S
THE EIGHTH CHILD?
Kari: HERE, MIKO!
[ CAT MEOWS ]
Mom: HELLO, KARI.
WE'RE BACK.
Dad: IS EVERYTHING
ALL RIGHT, SWEETIE?
HI. EVERYTHING'S JUST FINE.
[ MEOW ]
WHAT WAS WRONG
WITH GRANDMA?
SHE TOOK A BIT
OF A FALL.
SHE SPRAINED HER ANKLE
OUT FOR A WALK,
BUT IT'S NOT SERIOUS.
SHE HAS TO STAY
IN THE HOSPITAL FOR A DAY,
AND SHE'S MAD 'CAUSE IT
CUTS INTO HER DANCING LESSON.
THAT'S GRANDMA.
HERE.
THANKS, SWEET PEA.
[ MEOW ]
GRANDMA WORRIED
ABOUT YOUR COLD
AND SAID DADDY SHOULD
REMEMBER YOUR SWEATER.
GRR!
I FEEL
BACK TO NORMAL NOW.
OH? YOU LOOK
MUCH BETTER,
BUT LET'S MAKE SURE.
[ PURRING ]
YOU FEEL ABOUT AS COOL
AS A CUCUMBER.
[ GIGGLES ]
[ MEOW ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
I'M BACK! HI!
TAI?
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
CAMP WAS CANCELLED
BECAUSE IT SNOWED.
SNOW? WHO WOULD'VE THOUGHT
AT THIS TIME OF YEAR?
THE WEATHER'S GETTING
SO UNPREDICTABLE.
OH! WHAT'S THAT?
HUH? I BROUGHT KARI HOME
A PRESENT.
GREAT. GIVE ME
YOUR DIRTY CLOTHES
SO I CAN WASH THEM.
MOM!
[ Sobs ]
TAI, DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
OF COURSE I AM.
WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
[ MEOW ]
OH, SOMETHING WRONG?
DAD!
[ CRYING ]
HUH?
[ MEOW ]
[ MEOW MEOW ]
REALLY? I'M SURE
YOUR KIDS AREN'T THAT BAD.
Woman: I'm telling you,
you're lucky to have
a boy like Izzy.
He's a perfect example
of a gentleman
and so smart.
HA HA HA HA.
My little rascals are always
fighting all the time
and never listen
to a word I say.
Boy: Mom, tell Billy
to give me back my truck!
Woman: Mikey, don't stick
your tongue at your brother.
Izzy: I'M HOME!
IZZY?
HI, MOM. I CAME HOME
AHEAD OF SCHEDULE.
DIDN'T YOU LIKE CAMP?
HUH?
HA HA HA HA HA.
THE FOOD WAS INFERIOR.
THAT'S ALL?
AND THEN IT SNOWED,
SO THEY CANCELLED EVERYTHING.
[ BOYS CRYING
ON OTHER END OF LINE ]
Woman: Stop that!
They never think
about how I feel.
I wish they were
as considerate as Izzy.
SOMETIMES
HE'S TOO CONSIDERATE.
[ GRUNTS ]
HYAH!
SO WHY CAN'T
I USE THE DOOR?
Mom: IZZY,
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
HIDE!
WHAT AM I,
A MOLEMON?
I'M FINE, MOM!
HMM.
HUH.
Izzy: SEE YOU, MOM.
I'M GOING TO TAI'S HOUSE
FOR A WHILE.
HUH?
RIGHT NOW?
YEAH, I'M BORROWING ONE
OF HIS REFERENCE BOOKS.
I'LL BE BACK
IN A NANOSECOND.
Man: A SUSPICIOUS LIFE FORM
HAS BEEN SPOTTED IN THE BAY.
THERE IS SPECULATION THAT IT
IS SOME KIND OF MONSTER.
IT'S POSSIBLE
THAT IT COULD BE A WHALE,
BUT IT SEEMS UNLIKELY.
THERE MAY BE SOME CONNECTION
BETWEEN THIS MONSTER
AND THE GIANT ELEPHANT
AND BIRD
THAT ATTACKED A NEARBY TOWN.
TIME FOR SPORTS.
Izzy: I'M BACK!
DINNER'S ALMOST READY.
MY PARENTS
WON'T APPRECIATE THIS,
BUT I THINK
IT'S IMPERATIVE.
WHY? WHAT'S
THE BIG DEAL, IZZY?
WE'D BE IN BIG TROUBLE
IF MY MOM AND DAD
CAME IN HERE
AND DISCOVERED YOU.
I'M POSITIVE THEY'D NEVER
COMPREHEND OUR SITUATION.
YOU HAVE A POINT THERE.
BY THE WAY,
I DON'T KNOW TOO MUCH
ABOUT HUMANS,
ME BEING A DIGIMON
AND ALL,
BUT YOUR MOM
IS A REALLY KIND LADY,
AND IF YOU DON'T MIND
ME SAYING SO,
SHE'S NOT BAD-LOOKING
FOR A HUMAN.
MM-HMM, I HAVE TO SAY
I COMPLETELY AGREE.
SHE'S COOL.
ONE OF THESE DAYS,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO TELL IZZY THE TRUTH
ABOUT HIS BIRTH.
COULDN'T WE WAIT
A LITTLE LONGER?
I'M AFRAID
THAT IF WE TELL HIM NOW,
IT WILL BE TOO BIG
OF A SHOCK.
I WOULDN'T WANT IT
TO AFFECT HIS SCHOOLWORK.
BUT SOMETIMES I WONDER
IF HE DOESN'T SENSE IT.
HE'S SMART.
I HAVE A STRANGE FEELING
THAT HE KNOWS
HE WAS ADOPTED,
THAT HE'S NOT REALLY
OUR CHILD.
WHY DO YOU
THINK THAT, DEAR?
DID HE SAY ANYTHING?
NO, IT'S JUST
A MOTHER'S INTUITION.
YOO-HOO, DIGIMON TO IZZY.
HUH?
I'M SORRY, PAL.
I GUESS
I KIND OF ZONED OUT.
Woman: IZZY, ARE YOU IN THERE?
WHAT IS IT?
DINNER'S READY.
JUST A MINUTE.
IF YOU HAVE A FRIEND OVER,
HE CAN JOIN US, TOO.
I HEARD SOMEONE SPEAKING
IN A FUNNY-SOUNDING VOICE.
IS THAT WHAT I HEARD?
IZZY?
NO, I'M PRACTICING
MY NEW COMEDY ACT.
THEY'RE HAVING A TALENT SHOW
AT THE CHILDREN'S CENTER,
AND THE WINNER
COULD WIN A NEW COMPUTER.
YOU TELL JOKES?
[ SCREECHING ]
WHY WAS NEWTON SURPRISED
WHEN HE WAS HIT
ON THE HEAD BY AN APPLE?
HE WAS SITTING
UNDER A PEAR TREE.
WHAT'S BLACK AND WHITE
AND GREEN?
TWO SKUNKS FIGHTING
OVER A PICKLE.
I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I'M NOT VERY FUNNY.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU WERE HYSTERICAL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S MY SON.
MY BOY, THE COMEDIAN --
WHO WOULD HAVE KNOWN?
ALL THIS TIME, I NEVER KNEW
YOU HAD A SENSE OF HUMOR.
BRAVO, IZZY.
THAT WAS A GREAT PERFORMANCE
FOR YOUR FIRST TIME.
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
SURE THING.
YOU WERE REALLY GOOD.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE ABSOLUTELY THRILLED
FOR YOU, DARLING.
WELL, THANKS. OH.
OH.
UGH.
UH, MOM, WOULD YOU MIND
AT ALL IF I ATE THE REST
OF MY DINNER IN MY ROOM?
DON'T WORRY.
I WON'T MAKE YOU EAT ANYTHING
YOU DON'T WANT.
IT'S NOTHING LIKE THAT.
THE WAY YOU COOK
IS GASTRONOMICALLY OUTSTANDING.
THANKS.
I APPRECIATE
EVERYTHING YOU DO.
OH.
IN FACT,
I BELIEVE YOU'RE THE MOST
EXTRAORDINARY MOM THERE IS.
[ CHEWING AND GULPING ]
OH, I LEFT THE WATER ON.
[ LAUGHING ]
AHH.
MMM, MMM, MMM.
CAN I HAVE SOME MORE?
BUT, TAI,
THIS IS YOUR THIRD HELPING.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME SINCE
I'VE HAD SUCH GOOD COOKING.
HEY, MISTER,
IF YOU'RE BUTTERING ME UP
FOR A RAISE IN ALLOWANCE,
JUST FORGET ABOUT IT.
[ GULPING ]
NOT ONLY IS YOUR MOM
NICE AND PRETTY,
BUT SHE'S
AN AWESOME COOK.
DID YOU HEAR HIM?
HE SAID HE APPRECIATED US.
I NEVER THOUGHT
WE'D BE SO LUCKY
AS TO HAVE A SON LIKE HIM.
Man: YOU'RE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT, HONEY.
[ SCREECHING ]
[ WHINES ]
Koromon: WHAT IS IT, TAI?
YOU SEEM BUMMED.
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE BACK.
I MISSED YOU.
I MISSED YOU, TOO.
BY THE WAY, KARI,
DO YOU REMEMBER SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENED
ABOUT FOUR YEARS AGO
IN HIGHTON VIEW TERRACE?
TELL ME EVERYTHING YOU KNOW.
I REMEMBER
THAT KOROMON GOT REALLY HUGE
AND FOUGHT
WITH A BIG BIRD MONSTER.
AND HE BEAT HIM.
THAT'S SOMETHING
I'LL NEVER FORGET.
OH.
THIS MAY SOUND STRANGE,
BUT DO YOU HAVE SOMETHING
CALLED A DIGIVICE, KARI.
NO, WHAT'S THAT?
LIKE THIS.
DON'T THINK SO.
OH, WELL, FORGET ABOUT IT.
[ Yawns ]
I'M SO SLEEPY.
YEAH, I AM, TOO.
GOOD NIGHT.
SLEEP TIGHT, SLEEPYHEAD.
SWEET DREAMS.
YOU'RE PARTY POOPERS.
[ SNORING ]
OH, MIKO,
WHERE ARE YOU?
[ BEEPING ]
[ WHINES ]
THERE'S SOMETHING
BELOW THE SURFACE. HUH?
AAH!
YAY!
YEAH!
WHOO-HOO!
TALK ABOUT FINDING A NEEDLE
IN A HAYSTACK. SHEESH!
WHAT'S THAT? HE'S NEARBY.
THE EIGHTH CHILD
HAD BETTER WATCH OUT
'CAUSE HE'S A SITTING DUCK.
[ MEOW ]
[ SNORING ]
GENNAI MADE SOME MODIFICATIONS
TO MY COMPUTER
THAT ARE TRULY AWESOME.
WHOA.
NOW,
THIS LOOKS INTRIGUING.
I WONDER WHAT IT DOES.
WHOA -- TOO BIZARRE.
HOW ABOUT ANOTHER?
THAT'S VERY DEMENTED.
HERE'S SOMETHING.
IT'S A MAP OF TOKYO.
WHAT'S THAT INDICATOR?
There's an unidentified
digimon lurking in the bay.
You're the only one
that's still awake!
OH, TENTOMON!
[ GROWLS ]
HELLO, MRS. KAMIYA.
THIS IS IZZY.
I WAS WONDERING
IF TAI MIGHT BE AVAILABLE
TO COME TO THE PHONE.
HE'S SLEEPING.
SO WOULD YOU LIKE ME
TO WAKE HIM UP?
NO.
I'M SORRY TO BOTHER YOU.
I KNOW IT'S LATE,
BUT IS SORA AWAKE?
IS MATT HOME?
I'LL CALL BACK TOMORROW.
I GUESS EVERYONE'S ASLEEP.
YOU SHOULD
GO TO BED, TOO, IZZY.
NO WAY.
GENNAI JUST TOLD ME
THAT THERE'S AN UNIDENTIFIED
DIGIMON IN THE BAY.
WITH EVERYONE SOUND ASLEEP,
WE MAY HAVE TO TACKLE
THIS DIGIMON BY OURSELVES.
AND I WAS HAVING
SUCH A NICE DREAM.
YEAH!
OH!
AAH!
ARE YOU UP
FOR A CHALLENGE?
I'M WITH YOU, IZZY.
MAY I SUGGEST
I WEAR A DISGUISE
SO I DON'T ATTRACT
ANY UNWANTED ATTENTION?
[ MEOW ]
[ GROWLS ]
WHOA!
HE'S ABOUT AS REPULSIVE
AS THEY COME.
THAT DIGIMON IS RAREMON.
Tentomon: RAREMON SMELLS
LIKE ROTTING FISH,
LOOKS LIKE THE INSIDE
OF A TRASH CAN,
AND IS SOMEONE YOU NEVER WANT
TO MEET IN A VERY DARK ALLEY.
HUH?
WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S THE EIGHTH CHILD.
HE'S VERY CLOSE.
TALK ABOUT BAD TIMING.
IF WE LOSE THAT SIGNAL,
WE'LL BE DOOMED.
YOU SEARCH
FOR THE MISSING CHILD
WHILE I TAKE CARE
OF OLD SEWER BREATH.
YOU CAN DO IT!
DO I HAVE
ANY OTHER CHOICE?
ARE YOU READY TO DIGEVOLVE?
YEP.
TENTOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
KABUTERIMON!
GOOD LUCK!
IT'S MY TURN NOW.
HA HA HA HA!
TAI?
SWEETHEART, WAKE UP!
WHAT IS IT, MOM?
I DIDN'T WANT TO WAKE YOU,
BUT IZZY CALLED
AND HE SEEMED TO BE
NERVOUS ABOUT SOMETHING.
HUH?
I WONDER WHAT'S UP.
Raremon: [ GROWLS ]
ELECTRO SHOCKER!
BREATH OF DECAY.
[ MEOW ]
HUH? HE'S HERE!
HMM. OH. HUH?
THIS INDICATES
HE'S MOVING OVER THERE.
[ MEOW ]
HELLO, CAN I HELP YOU?
OH, HELLO, TAI. I HOPE
THAT YOU HAD FUN AT CAMP.
IT'S A SHAME
IT WAS CUT SHORT.
AND THANK YOU FOR LOANING
IZZY THAT REFERENCE BOOK.
[ GASPS ]
[ GROWLS ]
ELECTRO SHOCKER!
[ MEOW ]
IZZY, WE'D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU.
ARE YOU ASLEEP?
I'M SURE HE'S VERY
TIRED OUT FROM CAMP.
WE SHOULD LET HIM
GET A COUPLE OF Z's.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'LL JUST TIPTOE IN
AND CHECK UP ON HIM.
THE DOOR'S LOCKED!
HE'S CLOSE.
I'LL GET THERE FIRST.
AAH!
[ GROWLS ]
[ SNIFFING ]
AAH!
WE SHOULD BE
CONNECTING SOON.
OH, DON'T WORRY.
I'M SURE IT'S NOTHING
TO BE CONCERNED ABOUT.
I KNOW YOU'RE RIGHT,
BUT HE'S ACTING PECULIAR.
IZZY'S NEVER
LOCKED THE DOOR BEFORE.
HE IS GETTING OLDER.
I GUESS SO, BUT HE WAS
ONLY AT CAMP FOR HALF A DAY.
I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED
TO MAKE HIM CHANGE SO MUCH.
[ SQUAWKS ]
THE SIGNAL'S GONE NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUMBLING ]
AAH!
[ GROWLS ]
ELECTRO SHOCKER!
AAH!
HA HA HA HA!
[ GROWLS ]
OH, NO, IT'S BUG FACE!
I'M GOING TO GET YOU NEXT TIME!
I'M HERE AT THE SCENE
OF THE MONSTER SIGHTING,
BUT THE PREDATOR IN QUESTION
SEEMS TO HAVE DISAPPEARED.
ONE WONDERS IF THERE
REALLY WAS A MONSTER AT ALL.
HMM? WAIT A MINUTE, FOLKS.
LOOK UP THERE.
IT LOOKS LIKE
A GIANT FLYING COCKROACH,
AND I DON'T THINK
IT'S FRIENDLY.
SORRY YOU WEREN'T ABLE TO FIND
THE EIGHTH CHILD,
BUT AT LEAST WE GOT RID OF THAT
STINKING MASS OF BLUBBER.
Izzy: RIGHT. I'VE BEEN DOING
SOME EXTENSIVE CALCULATIONS.
MY THEORY IS THE EIGHTH CHILD
IS LOCATED HERE IN THE CITY.
IT SEEMS
TAI HAD THE RIGHT IDEA.
WE HAVE TO GET BACK TO HIS HOUSE
AND GIVE HIM AN UPDATE.
Kabuterimon: OKAY.
IS THERE NO DIGIMON
STRONG ENOUGH
TO DEFEAT THESE CHILDREN?
I WILL
DEAL WITH THEM MYSELF.
IT'S VERY LATE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD WAIT
UNTIL MORNING, TENTOMON.
ALL THAT EXERCISE
MADE ME ULTRA-HUNGRY.
I HATE TO BE A PIG,
BUT YOU WOULDN'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO MUNCH ON, WOULD YOU, IZZY?
YOU DESERVE A NUTRITION BREAK.
I'LL GO LOOK IN THE FRIDGE.
GEE, THANKS.
Woman:
EVER SINCE HE GOT BACK,
HE SEEMS LIKE
HE'S BEEN HIDING SOMETHING.
I CAN'T PUT MY FINGER ON IT.
HE'S KEEPING SOMETHING INSIDE.
HE DOESN'T WANT
TO TELL US WHAT'S WRONG.
YOU CAN'T BLAME HIM.
AFTER ALL, WE'RE HIDING
SOMETHING FROM HIM.
IT'S PROBABLY
JUST A PHASE.
[ Thinking ] I DIDN'T MEAN
TO MAKE THEM SO WORRIED.
I HOPE THEY FORGIVE ME.
I'M SURE HE'LL
BE ABSOLUTELY FINE,
BUT I'LL TRY TO TALK
SOME SENSE INTO HIM.
NO, DON'T.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
EVERYBODY THINKS
HE'S PERFECT,
BUT THAT'S TOO MUCH
TO EXPECT.
WE'VE GOT TO GIVE HIM FREEDOM
TO BECOME HIS OWN MAN.
HE'S GOT TO MAKE MISTAKES.
THAT'S PART OF WHAT IT IS
TO BE A KID.
DON'T YOU THINK SO?
[ SIGHS ]
I WONDER WHAT IZZY
WAS ALL HYPED UP ABOUT
WHEN HE CALLED TONIGHT.
WHAT HAPPENED TO MIKO?
HE DISAPPEARED.
OH, HE'LL BE BACK.
[ SIGHS ]
IT'S THE EIGHTH CHILD.
GOT TO GO!
THE EIGHTH WHAT?
OH, WHAT A PRETTY STAR.
[ SQUAWKING ]