Matt: WE FOUND MIMI LIVING
LIKE A PRINCESS IN A CASTLE
WITH A BUNCH OF FROGGY-LOOKING
GUYS CALLED GECKOMON.
THEY HAD THE IDEA THAT MIMI'S
SINGING COULD WAKE THEIR MASTER
FROM A KIND OF COMA, BUT MIMI
LOVED THE ROYAL TREATMENT.
SHE MADE UP EXCUSES WHY SHE
COULDN'T GET THROUGH HER SONG.
WHEN WE TOLD HER
TO STOP FOOLING AROUND,
SHE THREW US IN PRISON.
NICE, HUH?
SHE CAME TO HER SENSES
AND SANG HER SONG.
THE BIG GUY WOKE UP,
BUT IN A NASTY MOOD.
THANKS TO METALGRAYMON,
WE GOT OUT IN ONE PIECE.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
dú BEEMIDEVIMON'S
TRICKS, WE BECAME SEPARATED.
ONCE WE CAUGHT WIND
OF THAT BLOWHARD,
WE WERE ABLE
TO FIND EACH OTHER,
EXCEPT FOR SORA.
Tai: OKAY, WE'RE HERE.
OOH, I'M TIRED.
COME ON, MIMI.
GET OFF YOUR THRONE.
HA. I WOULD EXACTLY
CALL THIS A THRONE.
YEAH, WELL, I WOULDN'T
CALL YOU A PRINCESS.
Matt: GUYS, OVER HERE!
HEY, IT'S MATT.
IT'S BEEN SO LONG
SINCE I'VE SEEN YOU.
MY, YOU'VE SHRUNK.
All:
DON'T RUB IT IN.
WHERE'S SORA?
WE THOUGHT YOU MIGHT KNOW.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
THAT'S WEIRD.
IT'S NOT LIKE HER
TO DISAPPEAR LIKE THAT.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
I THINK I SAW SORA.
SO WHERE DID YOU SEE HER?
THE GECKOMON'S CASTLE.
I MIGHT HAVE BEEN DREAMING.
THAT-A-GIRL, I KNEW
YOU'D COME BACK TO YOURSELF.
Joe: YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN A DREAM.
ACTUALLY, I FORGOT
THAT WHEN I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO EAT ONE OF THOSE
MUSHROOMS OF FORGETFULNESS,
WHEN I WAS AGUMON,
I HEARD A VOICE
THAT SOUNDED A LOT
LIKE SORA'S.
Matt: THAT'S REAL WEIRD.
BUT THEN, IF SORA'S ACTUALLY
CLOSE TO WHERE WE ARE,
WHY DOESN'T SHE COME OUT
AND TELL US?
WELL, MAYBE SORA JUST
DOESN'T WANT TO.
EVEN WORSE,
MAYBE SHE JUST CAN'T.
[ DIGIVICE BEEPS ]
ALL I KNOW IS
WE'VE GOT TO FIND HER QUICK.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE WE'RE
PLAYING TAG WITH HER.
COME ON, THE SIGNAL
POINTS THIS WAY.
[ SCREAMING ]
BECAUSE OF YOUR STUPIDITY,
ALL OF MY EVIL PLANS
HAVE FAILED.
Demidevimon: OH BOY MYOTISMON.
HOW DID I GET STUCK WORKING
FOR THIS GUY?
TALK ABOUT A BAD TEMPER.
AND HE'S GOT ALL THOSE BATS.
I HATE BATS!
FORGIVE MY MISTAKES,
MASTER MYOTISMON.
I BEG YOU.
COURAGE,
HOPE, FRIENDSHIP --
THE CHILDREN'S CRESTS
ARE BEGINNING TO GLOW
ONE BY ONE.
EVERYONE MAKES MISTAKES.
REMEMBER DISCO?
BESIDES, SIR,
NOT ALL THE CHILDREN'S CRESTS
HAVE BEGUN TO GLOW YET.
THAT GIRL
HAS THE CREST OF LOVE,
AND IT'S STILL NOT GLOWING,
THANKS TO ME.
HEH HEH HEH.
ANYWAY, ACCORDING
TO MY SCHEDULE,
SHE'LL BE MEETING UP
WITH THE OTHER CHILDREN
VERY SOON.
AND WHEN SHE DOES,
MASTER MYOTISMON,
WHEN THEY ARE ALL TOGETHER,
THAT'S WHEN I'LL GET THEM.
YOU THINK YOU CAN?
IF YOU FAIL ME AGAIN,
MY BATS WILL HAVE
A NEW CHEW TOY --
YOU!
HA HA HA. I HATE BATS.
Matt: SORA!
T.K.: SORA,
WHERE ARE YOU?
Joe: WHY DON'T WE REST
FOR THE NIGHT, OR BETTER YET,
FOR THE NEXT COUPLE OF WEEKS?
MY FEET ARE KILLING ME,
NOT TO MENTION
EVERY OTHER PART OF MY BODY.
OH, I CAN'T
GO ANOTHER INCH.
HOLD IT.
I'M GETTING A READING
ON MY DIGIVICE.
T.K.: REALLY?
WELL, WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S THAT BUZZING?
I WONDER IF IT'S SORA?
Matt: WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
All: AAH!
FLYMON'S HERE!
BROWN STINGERS!
All: AAH!
MAYBE THIS DIGIMON ANALYZER
THE JENI GAVE ME
CAN HELP US OUT.
HERE HE IS -- FLYMON --
CLASSIFIED AS AN INSECT DIGIMON,
A VIRUS TYPE.
I THINK WE ALREADY KNOW
WHAT HIS ATTACK IS,
AND IT'S NOT VERY PLEASANT.
AND HERE HE COMES NOW!
All: AAH!
AAH!
CAREFUL, TAI!
WHOA!
LOOK OUT, MATT!
KOROMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
AGUMON.
TSUNOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GABUMON.
AGUMON.
PEPPER BREATH!
BLUE BLASTER!
JUST NOT WORKING
THEY NEED MORE HELP.
MARCHING FISHES!
POISON IVY!
BROWN STINGERS!
Both: AAH!
AAH!
[ SCREECHES ]
IT'S BIRDRAMON.
METEOR WING!
AAH!
IF BIRDRAMON'S HERE,
THEN SO IS SORA.
[ SCREECHES ]
SORA!
Agumon: WAIT UP, TAI.
T.K.: I'M GOING WITH YOU.
T.K., WAIT UP.
[ PANTING ]
SORA, IT'S YOU.
SO, WHY WERE YOU
RUNNING AWAY?
ENOUGH RUNNING.
TELL US WHAT'S GOING ON.
SORA?
[ PANTING ]
SORA,
DOES THIS MEAN
THAT YOU
DON'T LIKE US ANYMORE?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
THEN WHAT'S WRONG?
SORA, WHY DON'T
YOU TELL THEM?
OKAY, IT HAPPENED THE NIGHT
THAT BIYOMON AND I LEFT CAMP
TO TRY AND FIND TAI.
SHH. SOMEONE'S HERE.
HUH?
OH!
I SAW A STRANGE DIGIMON.
HE LOOKED
LIKE A BOWLING BALL WITH WINGS,
AND HE WAS TALKING
TO SOMETHING IN A GIANT BUBBLE.
COULD YOU HEAR?
YEAH, I HEARD TALKING
ABOUT OUR CRESTS.
WHAT ABOUT THEM?
HE WAS SAYING
THAT EACH OF OUR CRESTS
HAS ITS OWN
SPECIAL MEANING.
FOR EXAMPLE, TAI, YOURS IS
THE CREST OF COURAGE.
THE CREST OF COURAGE?
OH.
GATHER YOUR COURAGE.
THAT'S RIGHT, AND THEN
THE CREST STARTED TO GLOW.
THE CREST YOU HAVE, MATT,
IS THE CREST
OF FRIENDSHIP.
FRIENDSHIP?
AND MINE?
YOURS IS SPECIAL, T.K.
IT'S THE CREST OF HOPE.
ALL RIGHT. I HOPE
WE CAN GET BACK HOME.
IZZY'S CREST
IS THE CREST OF KNOWLEDGE.
JOE'S IS THE CREST
OF RELIABILITY.
THANKS FOR BEING THERE,
JOE.
AND MIMI'S IS THE CREST
OF SINCERITY.
AND FINALLY, MINE.
MINE IS THE CREST OF LOVE.
WOW, THE CREST OF LOVE.
THAT'S JUST PERFECT
FOR YOU, SORA.
NO, IT'S NOT.
YOU'RE WRONG!
DON'T SAY THAT.
IT'S NOT LIKE ME AT ALL.
BUT, SORA,
IT IS LIKE YOU.
YOU'RE ALWAYS THINKING
OF EVERYONE ELSE.
NO WAY! I DON'T CARE
WHAT HAPPENS TO EVERYONE ELSE.
THE TRUTH IS, YOU DON'T KNOW
THE FIRST THING ABOUT ME.
SO BACK OFF.
OH, I'M SORRY, TAI.
SORA, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IT'S JUST
THAT MY CREST --
IT WON'T GLOW.
HUH?
IT'S BECAUSE
I DON'T HAVE ANY LOVE.
T.K.: YOU LOVE US,
DON'T YOU, SORA?
I DON'T GET IT.
WHY IS IT THAT GIRLS
ALWAYS HAVE TO GET SO EMOTIONAL
WHEN IT COMES TO LOVE?
LEAVE HER ALONE, TAI.
I WAS JUST
JOKING AROUND.
THE DIGIMON
THOUGHT I WAS FUNNY, TOO.
IS YOUR NAME
BY ANY CHANCE DEMIDEVIMON?
IT SURE IS,
AND YOU'RE ONE
OF THOSE KIDS --
THE DIGIDESTINED.
TELL ME SOMETHING.
DID YOU HEAR ABOUT THE CRESTS?
YES, IN FACT, I DID.
OH, YEAH,
YOU'RE THAT KID SORA.
HEE HEE HEE HEE.
THE CREST OF LOVE.
AND WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING
ABOUT THAT?
YOU JUST THINK YOU'RE SO HOT,
BUT GUESS WHAT.
YOU'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO MAKE THE CREST GLOW,
NEVER!
OH, OH!
Tai: THAT'S IT? I THOUGHT
IT WAS SOMETHING SERIOUS,
LIKE THEY WERE GOING
TO STOP MAKING
THOSE STUFFED
BEANBAG ANIMALS.
BESIDES,
DEMIDEVIMON IS A LIAR.
IT'S TRUE.
IT STARTED BACK WHEN I WAS
ON A GIRLS' SOCCER TEAM.
MY FAMILY OWNED A FLOWER SHOP.
IT WAS MY MOM'S WHOLE LIFE.
MOM, I GOT TO GO
TO THE SOCCER MATCH.
THE GIRLS ARE COUNTING
ON ME.
DON'T TALK SO LOUD, DEAR.
THE FLOWERS
ARE VERY SENSITIVE.
BUT THIS MATCH IS
TO WIN THE TITLE.
SORA, YOU CAN'T GO
WITH YOUR KNEE INJURED
LIKE THAT.
BUT, MOM, MY LEG'S FINE.
I'M SORRY. YOU CAN'T GO.
SIT DOWN.
WE NEED TO TALK.
I WANT YOU TO STOP
PLAYING SOCCER AND COME
TO WORK AT THE FLOWER SHOP
AFTER SCHOOL.
DO WHAT?
I WON'T STOP PLAYING TO WORK
WITH SMELLY OLD FLOWERS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
A DAUGHTER OF MINE
WOULD ACT THIS WAY.
MY DECISION IS FINAL.
[ SOBBING ]
WHY CAN'T YOU
UNDERSTAND ME?
I WALKED AROUND FOR HOURS.
I FOUND MYSELF
AT THE SOCCER FIELD.
THE GAME HAD JUST FINISHED.
Matt: WHAT HAPPENED?
WE LOST THE GAME 6 TO 3.
MY TEAMMATES WERE SO DEPRESSED
THAT THEY DIDN'T NOTICE ME
WHEN THEY WALKED BY ME.
I FELT
LIKE I HAD LET THEM DOWN,
LIKE IT WAS ALL MY FAULT.
MY MOM SAID I HAD TO BE PART
OF THE FAMILY BUSINESS,
NO QUESTIONS.
THAT'S HOW SHE IS.
IT'S LIKE IT'S THE ONLY THING
THAT'S IMPORTANT TO HER.
SHE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND.
THAT'S WHY I KNOW
HE WASN'T LYING WHEN HE SAID
I GREW UP NOT KNOWING
WHAT LOVE IS.
STOP IT.
LET GO!
EVEN IF WHAT YOU SAID
IS TRUE,
YOU SHOULDN'T BELIEVE A WORD
FROM THAT LOSER DEMIDEVIMON.
HE'S JUST A CREEP
THAT'S TRYING TO HURT YOU.
[ CRYING ]
WAIT, WAIT.
DON'T CRY, SORA.
DON'T CRY, SORA. MATT, HELP.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH HER WHEN SHE
STARTS BLUBBERING.
JUST LET HER GO, TAI.
SHE'LL BE OKAY.
BOY, MATT'S LIKE
A REAL GROWN-UP.
NOW IF ONLY
HE WOULD CUT HIS HAIR.
SORA, I FORGOT
TO THANK YOU.
HUH?
YOU TOLD US NOT TO EAT
THE MUSHROOMS, DIDN'T YOU?
I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR SAVING US.
WE THOUGHT DEMIDEVIMON
WAS UP TO NO GOOD,
SO WE KEPT OUT OF SIGHT
AND MADE SURE
YOU GUYS
STAYED OUT OF TROUBLE.
WE WERE EVEN THERE
WHEN YOU GUYS WERE WORKING
IN THE RESTAURANT, MATT.
HUH?
I HAD NO IDEA.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO HIDE
FROM US.
WE WERE ALL WORRIED.
SORA JUST NEEDED TO BE ALONE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE,
BUT SHE REALLY DIDN'T WANT
TO BE SEPARATED FROM YOU GUYS.
PLEASE UNDERSTAND.
SORA, I LIKE YOU.
HUH?
SO, PLEASE,
DON'T GO AWAY AGAIN.
I DON'T LIKE
BEING AWAY FROM YOU.
HA HA. WHEN YOU'RE AROUND,
I DON'T MISS MY MOM AS MUCH.
T.K.
[ SOBBING ]
I'M SO, SO SORRY.
Joe: HEY.
HEY,
WHAT TOOK YOU GUYS SO LONG?
Mimi: WELL, WE WOULD HAVE
BEEN HERE SOONER,
BUT JOE FELL
IN THE RIVER.
Joe: HEY, MIMI, YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO WAS HUNGRY AND TIRED
AND HAD TO SIT DOWN
EVERY FIVE MINUTES.
FINALLY,
THEY'RE ALL TOGETHER.
I MUST TELL MYOTISMON.
[ ROARS ]
SOUND ASLEEP.
ALL RIGHT! HA!
MYOTISMON WILL BE SO PROUD
OF MY WORK,
MAYBE I'LL
GET A PROMOTION.
[ GASPS ]
DEMI DART!
SORA, WATCH OUT!
BIYOMON!
NO, BIYOMON,
PLEASE WAKE UP.
BIYOMON!
SORA, I WILL PROTECT YOU.
OH, NO.
SORA, WHAT'S WRONG?
OH, DEMIDEVIMON!
AAH!
HUH?
OH!
AAH!
HEY, WHAT IS THAT?
[ SNARLS ]
HA HA HA HA HA.
DIGIDESTINED,
YOUR JOURNEY ENDS HERE.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE THING
DEMIDEVIMON WAS TALKING TO.
HE'S NOT A THING.
HE'S LORD MYOTISMON.
MYOTISMON?
THAT'S LORD MYOTISMON.
HA HA HA HA HA.
THESE DIGIDESTINED ARE
MAKING ME FEEL A LITTLE BATTY.
GRISLY WING!
COME ON, GUYS. LET'S GO!
PEPPER BREATH!
BLUE BLASTER!
MOTIMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
TENTOMON.
SUPER SHOCKER!
BOOM BUBBLE, POP.
Mimi: THEY'RE STILL
COMING AFTER US.
AAH! AAH!
MIMI!
PALMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
TOGEMON!
LET ME TRY
TO GET MY POINT ACROSS.
NEEDLE SPRAY!
WAY TO GO.
GOMAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
IKKAKUMON!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
WOW! WAY TO GO!
YOU CAN'T DEFEAT ME
THAT EASILY.
CRIMSON LIGHTNING!
AAH!
HA HA HA HA HA.
[ ROARS ]
HA HA HA.
AAH!
OHH!
HA HA HA HA HA.
Joe: TAI,
HE'S JUST TOO STRONG FOR US.
NOW WHAT?
I'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING
TO HELP THEM.
HUH?
I'M THE ONLY ONE LEFT
TO FIGHT MYOTISMON.
Sora: IT'S NO USE.
YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING
IN YOUR CONDITION.
PLEASE UNDERSTAND, SORA.
I HAVE TO GO.
BIYOMON, YOU CAN'T.
YOU'LL GET HURT.
I WON'T LET YOU.
MY DECISION IS FINAL.
SORA, WHY CAN'T
YOU UNDERSTAND?
HUH?
WHY CAN'T
YOU UNDERSTAND?
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
MY MOM WAS THINKING
ABOUT HER FLOWER SHOP,
BUT SHE WAS REALLY WORRIED
ABOUT ME GETTING HURT.
BIYOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
BIRDRAMON!
OH!
[ SCREECHES ]
METEOR WING!
CRIMSON LIGHTNING!
BIRDRAMON!
[ WAILS ]
BIRDRAMON, NO!
I LOVE YOU!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
BIRDRAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
GARUDAMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
WHAT? WHERE IS
THAT GLOW COMING FROM?
SORA, I CAN FEEL YOUR LOVE.
IT'S MAKING ME STRONG.
MY CREST -- IT GLOWS.
GARUDAMON IS THE ULTIMATE FORM
OF BIRDRAMON.
SHE COMMANDS THE SKY
AND PROTECTS THE EARTH.
HER ATTACK IS A FLAMING BIRD
CALLED WING BLADE.
AH, WHY IS IT NOW
THE CREST OF LOVE GLOWS
JUST AS I WAS ABOUT
TO CLAIM VICTORY?
I'LL PROTECT YOU, SORA.
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
WING BLADE!
♪ CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
[ Growls ] GRISLY WING!
I DID NOT ANTICIPATE
SUCH STRENGTH.
COME ON, EVERYONE.
CLIMB ON.
HUH?
NEXT TIME,
YOU WON'T ESCAPE.
Tai: ALL YOU HAD TO DO
WAS STOP WORRYING ABOUT IT,
SORA, AND YOU GOT
YOUR CREST TO WORK.
Sora: WHEN BIYOMON WAS
IN DANGER OF GETTING HURT,
I REALIZED THAT I WAS ACTING
JUST LIKE MY MOM.
KNOW WHAT I REALIZE?
MY MOM
LOVED ME ALL ALONG.
AND IT WAS YOUR LOVE
THAT HELPED ME
DIGEVOLVE, SORA.
I'M GLAD.
YOU SEE? YOU ARE CAPABLE
OF LOVE AFTER ALL.
I FELT SOMETHING. IT WAS
YOUR LOVE SHINING THROUGH.
I FELT SOMETHING, TOO.
IT MADE ME UNCOMFORTABLE.
LOVE SHOULDN'T MAKE YOU
FEEL LIKE THAT.
Mimi: THAT'S RIGHT.
I KNOW WHY YOU
FELT UNCOMFORTABLE, JOE.
THESE WERE IN YOUR POCKET.
OH, I GUESS IT WASN'T LOVE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Matt: SORA JOINED UP
WITH US AGAIN,
AND WE WERE CLOSER THAN EVER.
WE FINALLY THOUGHT THINGS
WERE GOING OUR WAY, AND THEN...
HUH?
[ MYOTISMON LAUGHS ]
I KNOW THAT LAUGH.
Myotismon: YOU FOOLISH
DIGIDESTINED.
THE SEVEN OF YOU
ARE NO MATCH FOR MY POWERS.
PREPARE
FOR YOUR ULTIMATE DESTRUCTION!
HA HA HA HA HA!