Matt: TAI LEFT HIS SISTER KARI
WHILE HE WAS OFF
PLAYING THE HERO.
IZZY SNUCK
INTO THE TV STATION
TO SABOTAGE
MYOTISMON'S FOG BARRIER.
JOE AND T.K. WERE TRYING
TO GET HOME.
MEGASIDRAMON WAS GUARDING
THE HARBOR.
IKKAKUMON DIGEVOLVED TO ZUDOMON
AND SAVED JOE.
THE KID AND I
WERE SITTING ON OUR HANDS.
PHANTOMON SHOWED UP,
AND THINGS GOT VERY INTENSE.
KARI TOLD THE CREEP
SHE WAS THE EIGHTH CHILD,
AND SHE'D GO WITH HIM
IF HE'D LEAVE US ALONE.
HOW AM I GOING
TO EXPLAIN THIS TO TAI?
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
KARI, YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING!
YOU CAN'T GIVE YOURSELF UP
TO MYOTISMON!
HE'LL DESTROY YOU
AND GAIN CONTROL OF BOTH WORLDS!
KARI, NO! UNH!
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
YES, IT IS.
I BLEW IT.
TAI ASKED ME
TO PROTECT HER,
AND I COULDN'T.
I LET EVERYONE DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MATT,
IT SEEMS TO ME
THERE ARE TWO THINGS
YOU CAN DO ABOUT THIS.
YOU CAN STAND THERE
AND BEAT YOURSELF UP,
OR WE CAN FIND A WAY
TO RESCUE KARI.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET'S GET HER.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
HURRY, AGUMON!
THE CONVENTION CENTER
IS UP AHEAD.
THAT'S WHERE MY PARENTS
ARE BEING HELD PRISONER.
AND KEEP AN EYE OUT
FOR MYOTISMON.
HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
[ CHILDREN GROANING ]
Myotismon: WELL, GATOMON,
IS THIS THE EIGHTH CHILD?
MNH-MNH.
MYOTISMON.
WHAT?
YOU'LL LOVE THIS, BOSS.
I FOUND THE EIGHTH DIGIDESTINED.
YOU DID?
HUH?
WHAT? HOW?
[ Thinking ]
OH, NO. NOT KARI.
YOU HEAR THAT? IT'S OVER.
GRR.
WELL, I HAVE NO USE
FOR THESE
LITTLE BRATS ANYMORE.
WHAT SHOULD I DO WITH THEM,
O EVIL ONE?
MAKE THEM GO TO SLEEP.
I'LL FIND A WAY
TO DEAL WITH THEM LATER.
[ MYOTISMON LAUGHING ]
MYOTISMON.
WHERE COULD HE BE GOING?
[ SNORING ]
UH?
MM.
[ MOANING ]
OH!
AAH!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS... ♪
AGUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GREYMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
NOVA BLAST!
[ SCREAMING ]
THEY DIDN'T STAND
A GHOST OF A CHANCE.
TAI, YOU MADE IT INSIDE!
MIMI, WHERE ARE THE OTHERS?
THEY'RE ALL FAST ASLEEP.
MYOTISMON PUT THEM UNDER
SOME KIND OF SPELL
SINCE HE FOUND
THE EIGHTH CHILD.
OH, NO! HE'S GOT KARI.
HUH? KARI?
LET'S GO!
HEY, LOOK!
THERE'S MATT AND SORA.
WHAT? MATT?
WHAT'S HE DOING HERE?
AAH! MONSTERS!
ACTUALLY, SIR,
THE TECHNICAL NAME
IS "DIGIMON."
YOU SEE, THEY'RE NOT LIKE
THE PRETEND MONSTERS
YOU'VE SEEN
IN THOSE OLD MOVIES
DESTROYING A BUNCH
OF JAPANESE CITIES.
MAYBE THAT'S
A BAD EXAMPLE,
BUT ANYWAY,
THE DIGIMON MATT'S RIDING
IS DEFINITELY ON OUR SIDE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"OUR SIDE?"
WELL, YOU SEE,
THERE ARE GOOD DIGIMON
AND BAD DIGIMON.
THE GOOD DIGIMON
ARE OUR FRIENDS,
JUST LIKE TENTOMON HERE.
I'M MORE THAN GOOD.
I'M EXCEPTIONAL.
I WOULDN'T DARE
DOUBT YOU.
BUT, JOE,
WHY DOES WIZARDMON
HAVE A TAG AND A CREST?
HMM.
HE SAID IT BELONGED
TO THE EIGHTH DIGIDESTINED.
THINK IT COULD BE TRUE?
HMM?
ARE YOU AWAKE?
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M T.K.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
KARI!
WHERE'S KARI?
KARI?
WHO'S KARI?
YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE
THIS CREST TO KARI.
YOU WANT US TO GIVE THAT
TO TAI'S
LITTLE SISTER KARI?
BUT IF WE HAVE TO DELIVER
THE CREST TO KARI,
THEN THAT MUST MEAN
SHE'S THE EIGHTH
DIGIDESTINED CHILD
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR
ALL ALONG!
GEE! I'M ALWAYS
THE LAST ONE TO FIND OUT.
WE HAVE NO TIME TO WASTE.
KARI AND GATOMON
NEED THIS CREST.
GATOMON?
BUT SHE'S ONE
OF THE BAD DIGIMON
THAT WORKS
FOR MYOTISMON!
YOU SAYING GATOMON
IS ONE OF THE GOOD GUYS?
EXACTLY.
HUH?
MATT! SORA!
HEY, YOU GUYS! HEY!
Sora: IZZY, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
MATT!
DAD.
I TOLD YOU
TO STAY OUT OF SIGHT.
I'M SORRY, DAD.
[ GROWLS ]
AAH!
HELLO, MATT'S DAD.
GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN "AGAIN"?
WHO ARE YOU? HAVE WE MET?
YOU KNOW ME.
I DIGEVOLVED
FROM GABUMON.
GABUMON? THAT'S YOU?
JOE! T.K.!
HEY, MATT! DADDY!
T.K.
OH, T.K.
DAD!
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
WHEN I SAW ALL THAT STUFF
ON TELEVISION,
I JUST COULDN'T
STAY HOME ANYMORE.
MOM WANTED TO COME, TOO,
BUT WE COULDN'T BRING HER.
IT'S OKAY, SON.
I MISSED YOU, DADDY.
Izzy: IT'S WIZARDMON.
Matt: WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
HMM. SHE WAS ATTACKED
BY MYOTISMON, WASN'T SHE?
SO WHAT IF SHE WAS?
HUH?
UH!
OH!
LILLYMON!
MM. WHAT'S THIS?
WIZARDMON?
HI-YAH!
STOP! DON'T ATTACK HIM!
WIZARDMON'S A GOOD DIGIMON!
HE'S GOT THE TAG AND CREST!
T.K., HE COULD
BE LYING.
NO, SORA,
IT'S ALL TRUE.
JUST LOOK.
OHH.
THIS TAG AND CREST
BELONG TO KARI.
HUH?
WE'VE GOT TO HELP GATOMON.
SHE WAS CAPTURED
BY MYOTISMON.
GATOMON?
YEAH.
WIZARDMON SAID GATOMON
BELONGS WITH KARI.
WHAT?
NOW, WHERE IS KARI?
WELL?
HE'S GOT HER.
GENNAI SENT ME SOME E-MAIL
A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
IF I RECALL CORRECTLY,
HE SAID THE TV STATION
IS THE CENTER
OF MYOTISMON'S
FOG BARRIER.
HEY, LOOK!
IT'S MYOTISMON!
[ BATS SCREECHING ]
AND HE'S GOT GATOMON...
HA HA HA HA.
BUT NOT FOR LONG.
COME ON, LET'S HEAD
FOR THE VIEWING PLATFORM.
RIGHT.
I'LL SHOW YOU THE WAY.
AAH!
[ GROWLING ]
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
GARURUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGEVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS... ♪
WEREGARURUMON!
[ HOWLS ]
LEAVE THIS BATTLE TO US.
WE CAN HANDLE
THESE DIGICLOWNS.
WE'LL GET KARI.
COME ON, EVERYONE,
LET'S GO!
UNH. OOH.
WIZARDMON,
ARE YOU OKAY?
LET ME GIVE YOU A HAND.
HERE.
[ BATS SCREECHING ]
OH. OH!
OHH.
I'VE GOT YOU, MY PRETTY,
AND YOUR LITTLE CAT, TOO.
HA HA HA HA HA HA HA!
[ GROWLING ]
WHAT'S THAT?
GREYMON, HURRY!
THEY NEED YOUR HELP.
YOU GOT IT!
LITTLE GIRL,
WHY HAVE YOU CHOSEN
TO SHOW YOURSELF TO ME?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT'S ABOUT TO HAPPEN?
I'VE GOT A GUESS.
THEN WHY?
'CAUSE YOU WERE HURTING
ALL THOSE PEOPLE.
HUH?
SOMEONE HAD TO STOP YOU
FROM HURTING INNOCENT PEOPLE!
HMM?
[ CHUCKLES ]
MY, WHAT A THOUGHTFUL
LITTLE GIRL YOU ARE.
GATOMON, WHY WON'T YOU LOOK
AT THE EIGHTH CHILD'S FACE?
BECAUSE SHE'S NOT
THE EIGHTH CHILD.
WHO IS SHE?
I'VE NEVER SEEN HER
BEFORE IN MY LIFE.
IS THAT RIGHT?
[ KARI SCREAMS ]
KARI! NO!
OW! MY HAIR!
KARI.
INTERESTING
THAT YOU KNOW HER NAME,
SINCE YOU'VE NEVER
MET HER BEFORE.
[ WHIMPERS ]
HURRY. IT'S UP HERE.
GOT IT, DAD.
WAIT HERE.
THANKS FOR THE HELP.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
DIGIMON HEAL FAST.
KARI!
TOGETHER AGAIN.
TOO BAD IT WILL BE
SHORT-LIVED.
HA HA HA HA HA.
GRISLY WING!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
TENTOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
KABUTERIMON!
ELECTROSHOCKER!
FLOWER CANNON!
[ SCREAMING ]
IT'S GETTING
A LITTLE NOISY IN HERE.
LET'S FIND
SOMEPLACE QUIETER.
[ GRUNTING ]
NOT SO FAST!
WEREGARURUMON!
UNH!
AAH!
HMM?
[ GROWLS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
I AM REALLY GETTING SICK
OF THAT LAUGH.
[ GROWLS ]
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
KABUTERIMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGEVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS,
DIGIMON ♪
MEGAKABUTERIMON!
[ ROARS ]
[ GROWLS ]
WE NEED YOU!
GET KARI! MEGAKABUTERIMON, GO!
[ GROWLS ]
HORN BLASTER!
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
HA! CRIMSON LIGHTNING!
AAH!
WEREGARURUMON!
OH, THAT'S GOT TO HURT.
AAH! OOH.
GRR.
WHAT?
KARI, HERE!
CATCH!
OH.
IT'S WIZARDMON!
SO, YOU'RE STILL ALIVE?
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'LL TAKE MORE THAN YOU
TO DESTROY ME.
WE WILL SEE.
AAH!
OHH.
NO! WIZARDMON!
NOW GIVE THAT TO ME,
YOU LITTLE BRAT.
NO!
THAT WASN'T A REQUEST.
Tai: WAIT!
MIMI.
YOU JUST PICKED ON
THE WRONG GUY'S LITTLE SISTER!
KARI, HERE! CATCH!
OH!
YEAH!
HEY.
THE DIGIVICE!
YOU CAN THANK ME
AFTER YOU TAKE OVER THE WORLD.
THAT'S NICE WORK.
GO GET THEM,
PHANTOMON!
[ MOANING ]
HUH?
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
GREYMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGEVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
METAL GREYMON!
[ ROARS ]
♪ DIGIMON ♪
TIME OUT!
GO GET HIM,
METAL GREYMON!
GIGABLASTER!
[ CHUCKLES ]
BUT HOW?
[ LAUGHS ]
HORN BLASTER!
VULCAN'S HAMMER!
WING BLADE!
FLOWER CANNON!
HA HA HA HA HA.
HE'S STRONG -- TOO STRONG.
MM-HMM.
ARE YOU DONE? I'M BORED.
IT'S TIME TO FINISH YOU OFF.
HMM!
NIGHTMARE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
PATAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
ANGEMON!
UH, NOW WHAT?
HAND OF FATE! GRR!
AAH!
HAVE YOU HAD ENOUGH,
OR DO YOU WANT
SOME MORE?
ACTUALLY, I WAS ABOUT
TO ASK YOU THE SAME QUESTION.
GRISLY WING!
[ SCREECHING ]
KARI!
NEXT TIME,
DON'T GET IN MY WAY.
OH, NO!
WIZARDMON,
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
ALL RIGHT.
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE.
WIZARDMON!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
GATOMON?
YOU SAVED ME.
I'M SORRY.
ABOUT WHAT?
SORRY I GOT YOU
INVOLVED IN THIS.
DON'T BE SORRY.
I DON'T HAVE ANY REGRETS.
IF I HADN'T MET YOU,
MY LIFE WOULD HAVE
HAD NO MEANING.
I'M GLAD THAT YOU AND I
WERE FRIENDS.
THAT'S FOREVER.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING,
GATOMON.
WIZARDMON,
ARE YOU OKAY?
PLEASE ANSWER.
WAAH!
LOOK!
IT'S KARI'S DIGIVICE!
I CAN'T HOLD ON! AAH!
KARI, HERE!
NOT HER! NO!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
GATOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGEVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
ANGEWOMAN!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
GATOMON IS AN ANGEL?
WHOA!
[ GASPING ]
MYOTISMON,
YOU'VE TRIED TO DESTROY
THE DIGIDESTINED
AND ATTEMPTED
TO CONQUER EARTH.
IN DOING SO,
YOU HAVE RUINED THE LIVES
OF DIGIMON AND HUMANS ALIKE.
HOW CAN
YOU JUSTIFY YOURSELF?
I DON'T HAVE TO
EXPLAIN MYSELF TO YOU.
IT IS MY DESTINY
TO PLUNGE THIS WORLD
INTO DARKNESS
AND BECOME KING
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD,
AND NO ANGEL OR DIGIMON
HAS THE POWER TO STOP ME.
DON'T YOU HAVE
ANY REGRETS
FOR THE THINGS
YOU HAVE DONE?
HA! NIGHTMARE!
HEAVEN'S CHARM!
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ THE MONSTER FRIENDS
TO THE BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON... ♪
MY POWER,
IT'S -- IT'S GROWING!
GRR! NO!
EVERYONE GIVE YOUR POWER
TO ANGEWOMAN.
HORN BLASTER!
FLOWER CANNON!
VULCAN'S HAMMER!
WOLF CLAW!
WING BLADE!
GIGABLASTER!
HAND OF FATE!
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ THE MONSTER FRIENDS
TO THE BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
CELESTIAL ARROW!
♪ CHAMPIONS OF
THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
NO! DON'T!
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
AHH!
[ GASPS ]
MYOTISMON IS GONE.
KARI!
ALL RIGHT! WE DID IT!
WHOA!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE WE'RE CRUSHED!
Tai: YOU GUYS ARE THE BOMB!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE FINALLY DESTROYED MYOTISMON.
THAT WASN'T SO TOUGH
AFTER ALL. GREAT!
YEAH.
HOPEFULLY,
NOW THE REAL WORLD
WILL RETURN TO NORMAL.
HEY, YOU TWO,
WHAT'S WRONG?
HUH?
LOOK UP THERE.
WHAT IS IT?
THE FOG --
IT'S GETTING THICKER.
IMPOSSIBLE. HUH?
HUH?
Kari: BUT MYOTISMON
IS GONE.
Tai: MAYBE NOT.
MAYBE HE'S STILL OUT THERE
SOMEWHERE.
WHAT IF WE JUST MADE HIM
STRONGER?
Narrator:
IS MYOTISMON TRULY GONE,
OR HAS HE DIGEVOLVED
TO A MORE POWERFUL FORM?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS."