IT'S SAD SOMEONE
COULD BE SO DEPRESSED
IT TAKES OVER THEIR LIFE.
FOR MATT, THESE FEELINGS
TOOK THE FORM OF A DEEP CAVE.
GABUMON FINALLY
OPENED MATT'S EYES
AND PROVED
HE WAS REALLY LOVED.
SORA HAD A SIMILAR PROBLEM,
BUT MATT AND JOE WERE ABLE
TO PULL HER OUT.
TAI AND WARGREYMON
HAD BEEN HOLDING OFF PIEDMON,
AND THEY WERE EXHAUSTED.
WITH THE POWER FROM MATT'S
CREST OF FRIENDSHIP,
THEY BECAME RE-ENERGIZED,
AND SHOULD TAKE CARE
OF THAT LAUGHING FOOL
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
NOW THAT WE HAVE
TWO MEGADIGIMON,
LET'S DESTROY PIEDMON
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
GO GET HIM,
METAL GARURUMON.
COME ON, WARGREYMON.
TAKE CARE OF THIS CLOWN.
SO I'M A CLOWN?
THEN I'LL ACT LIKE ONE.
CLOWN TRICK!
I'LL GET HIM.
TRY JUMPING
THROUGH THIS HOOP.
RRAAH!
ARE YOU OKAY?
Piedmon: WHY DON'T YOU
JOIN US? WE'RE HAVING A BALL.
HA HA! SORRY IF I
CAUGHT YOU OFF-BALANCE.
ROUND AND ROUND HE GOES.
WHERE HE LANDS,
NOBODY KNOWS.
HA HA HA!
[ GASPS ]
HE THINKS THIS
IS A GAME.
WELL, I'M TIRED
OF PLAYING AROUND.
LET'S NOT BE HASTY. HE WANTS
US TO MAKE A MISTAKE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DON'T WANT TO PLAY ANYMORE?
TRUMP SWORDS!
BE CAREFUL
OF THE SWORDS!
WAIT. SOME OF THOSE
AREN'T REAL.
WARGREYMON, I'M PICKING UP
THE REAL SWORDS
ON MY SENSORS,
OVER TO YOUR RIGHT.
COVER ME.
[ GRUNTS ]
Piedmon: HA HA!
METAL WOLF SNOUT!
[ GROWLS ]
LOOKS LIKE THE JOKE'S
ON YOU, PIEDMON.
TERRA FORCE!
AAH!
ALL RIGHT. NICE SHOT.
IZZY, HAVE EVERYONE
DIGEVOLVE AND ATTACK.
YOU HEARD HIM, GUYS.
NOW IT'S OUR TURN.
I'M IN.
ME TOO.
CAUTION.
A WHITE FLAG?
MAYBE HE'S TRYING
TO SURRENDER TO US.
Sora: I DON'T TRUST HIM.
I THINK HE'S GOT
ANOTHER TRICK UP HIS SLEEVE.
HA HA!
WHY DON'T YOU MAKE
YOURSELF DISAPPEAR?
PLAYTIME IS OVER.
BUT I'M
JUST GETTING STARTED.
RRAAH!
Matt: WARGREYMON!
Tai: METAL GARURUMON!
HA HA HA!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHOA!
WHAT HAPPENED?
I DON'T KNOW.
TA-DA!
THANKS FOR COMING.
YOU'VE BEEN A GREAT CROWD.
HE MADE THEM DISAPPEAR.
AT LEAST HE DIDN'T
SAW THEM IN HALF.
WHAT DID YOU DO
TO TAI AND MATT?
I HOLD THE KEYS
TO THEIR EXISTENCE,
AND I NEED A PLACE
TO PUT THEM,
SO I MADE A COUPLE
OF KEY CHAINS.
I THINK I'LL HANG THESE TWO
ON MY BACKPACK.
WHAT KIND OF SICKO
TURNS PEOPLE INTO KEY CHAINS?
I'M NOT A SICKO,
I'M A COLLECTOR,
AND THESE NEW ITEMS HAVE
SUCH SENTIMENTAL VALUE TO ME.
HA HA HA!
AH HA, AH HA HA HA!
NOW, WHO WANTS TO BE NEXT?
Centaurumon:
LOOK AT ALL THIS FIRE.
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
I DIDN'T BRING
A SINGLE MARSHMALLOW.
Centaurumon, I came
as fast as I could.
OH, GENNAI.
I'M GLAD YOU MADE IT.
Is this it?
YES. THIS IS
THE MYSTICAL WALL OF FIRE
THE ANCIENT PROPHECY
ON FILE ISLAND DESCRIBES.
Really? What do you say
we barbecue?
Incredible.
Is it really true
that he had to make it
across these flames?
I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY,
GENNAI,
BUT THAT'S WHAT
THE PROPHECY SAYS.
Unbelievable.
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
Andrumon: QUICK.
GET INTO THAT CAVE.
ANDRUMON!
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL HOLD HIM OFF.
LIGHTNING BLADE!
UHH!
[ GRUNTING ]
Sora: ANDRUMON!
WE'VE GOT TO GET
OUT OF HERE, SORA.
ANDRUMON'S BUYING US
MORE TIME.
AAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
GATLING ATTACK!
AAH!
HUH?
Voice: WHAT KIND OF PLACE
IS THIS?
Sora: IT LOOKS LIKE
A GIANT CIRCUS TENT.
Joe: WHATEVER IT IS,
I DON'T LIKE IT.
HEY! THERE'S A WAY OUT
ACROSS THIS CANYON.
MY ONLY QUESTION IS
HOW DO WE GET TO IT?
USE THESE SWINGS
LIKE A TRAPEZE ARTIST,
BUT DON'T LOOK DOWN.
THERE'S NO NET.
KARI, HOLD ME TIGHT
AND DON'T LET GO.
Kari: OHH!
NOT SO EASY TO FLY,
IS IT?
AAH!
Gatomon: WHAT DO YOU CARRY
IN THAT BACKPACK, BRICKS?
OW! GATOMON, YOU'VE GOT
TO TRIM YOUR CLAWS!
AWAY YOU GO!
AAH!
Piedmon: DON'T YOU WANT
TO TAKE YOUR FRIEND ALONG?
ANDRUMON! GO, IZZY.
AAH! JOE, HELP!
DON'T WORRY, IZZY.
I'LL SAVE YOU. OHH!
NOW YOU SEE THEM,
AND NOW YOU DON'T.
THEY'RE DROPPING
LIKE FLIES.
OH, MIMI,
I'M GETTING EXHAUSTED.
REALLY? THAT'S STRANGE.
I FEEL FRESH AS A DAISY.
[ GROANING ]
MIMI, GET UP HERE!
THE BATTLE'S STARTED!
OH, IT'S JUST MY LUCK --
I BRING REINFORCEMENTS,
AND ALL THEY WANT TO DO
IS HANG AROUND.
HELLO. MY NAME IS IZZY,
AND I'M VERY SMART,
ALTHOUGH I DIDN'T KNOW HOW
TO STOP ME AND MY FRIENDS
FROM BEING MADE
INTO KEY CHAINS!
HA HA HA! I LOVE
A GOOD PUPPET SHOW.
AAH!
OHH!
OHH! OHH!
AH, SO YOU WANT TO PLAY
HIDE-AND-GO-SEEK, HMM?
OKAY. I LOVE A GOOD GAME.
NOW, LET'S SEE.
IF I WERE A LITTLE PEST,
WHERE WOULD I HIDE, HMM?
MAYBE YOU'RE IN THIS ROOM
OVER HERE.
I THINK WE'RE
OUT OF DANGER FOR NOW.
AAH!
PEEK-A-BOO!
All: AAH!
RUN FOR IT!
Piedmon: OLLY, OLLY,
OXEN-FREE!
Angewoman: CELESTIAL ARROW!
RUN, KARI!
HURRY, SORA!
IT'S ANGEWOMAN!
GARUDAMON!
WINGED BLADE!
AAH!
Together: AAH!
T.K., COME HERE.
WHAT IS IT?
TAKE KARI
AND GET OUT OF HERE.
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU?
LISTEN,
THERE ISN'T MUCH TIME.
PIEDMON HAS OUR FRIENDS,
AND IF HE GETS US,
WE'RE DOOMED.
T.K., PLEASE.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN PROTECT KARI.
BE BRAVE. NOW GET GOING.
I WON'T LEAVE YOU.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'LL BE FINE.
ALL RIGHT.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
JUST KEEP RUNNING.
OKAY, SORA. I PROMISE
I'LL DO WHATEVER I CAN
TO PROTECT KARI.
RIGHT. HURRY. GO!
COME ON, KARI. LET'S GO.
SORA, I WANT TO STAY
AND FIGHT WITH YOU.
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
YOU CAN'T EVEN DIGEVOLVE
WITHOUT JOE,
SO GO BEFORE PIEDMON
GETS HERE.
JOE RISKED HIS NECK
TO PROTECT US.
IF PIEDMON
TURNS YOU INTO A DOLL,
HIS SACRIFICE
WILL MEAN NOTHING.
HELP T.K. AND KARI.
THERE'S NOT MUCH TIME!
[ GROANS ]
NOW GO!
AAH!
HA HA HA!
LOOK. I ONLY NEED
FIVE MORE KEY CHAINS,
AND I'LL HAVE
THE WHOLE SET.
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
UHH!
SORA!
T.K., CATCH!
IN ORDER TO SUCCEED,
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO STEP
ON PEOPLE ALONG THE WAY.
QUICK, LET'S RUN!
WE JUST RAN
OUT OF ROOM.
THIS ISN'T THE ESCAPE PLAN
I HAD IN MIND.
NOW WHAT?
CAN WE JUMP?
IT'S TOO FAR.
HA HA HA!
WELCOME TO THE DEAD END.
COME BE A KEY CHAIN
LIKE YOUR FRIEND.
WE CAN'T JUST SIT HERE.
WE HAVE TO CLIMB DOWN.
IT'S TOO HIGH, T.K.
IF WE SLIP, WE'RE GONERS.
T.K.: KARI, WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO TRY.
LOOK, T.K. WHERE'D
THAT BASKET COME FROM?
WHO PUT THAT THERE?
A ROPE!
WE CAN USE IT TO CLIMB DOWN
THE SIDE OF THE MOUNTAIN.
AAH!
Patamon: I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE A SNAKE-CHARMER.
Kari: THINK WE SHOULD
CLIMB IT?
T.K.: MOM SAID NEVER TAKE
CANDY OR ROPE FROM STRANGERS.
HA HA HA!
WHAT AM I THINKING?
WE HAVE TO CLIMB IT.
SORA TOLD ME TO BE BRAVE
NO MATTER HOW SCARED I GET.
LOOKS DANGEROUS.
YOU GO FIRST.
[ GRUNTING ]
THAT'S IT, KARI.
PRETEND YOU'RE IN GYM CLASS.
[ GRUNTING ]
LISTEN!
OPEN!
AAH!
THIS COSTS ME A FORTUNE
IN NEW DOORS.
KEEP CLIMBING.
I'LL DISTRACT HIM.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
PATAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
ANGEMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
[ GRUNTING ]
AAH!
YOU GET HIM, ANGEMON!
HAND OF FATE! HYAH!
CLOWN TRICK!
AAH!
ANGEMON, NO!
CLOWN TRICK!
AAH!
TRUMP SWORD!
DON'T GIVE UP!
AAH!
UNH!
ANGEMON, NO!
I'M SCARED.
IT'S OKAY.
[ Thinking ] GREAT.
NOW KARI'S AFRAID.
I CAN'T LET HER SEE
THAT I AM, TOO.
I'VE GOT TO BE BRAVE.
ANGEMON WILL BE FINE,
BUT KEEP ON CLIMBING.
DON'T LET THAT JOKER
PIEDMON SCARE YOU.
OKAY.
AAH!
Piedmon: YOU'VE REACHED
THE END OF YOUR ROPE! HA HA HA!
[ GROANS ]
T.K.!
NO!
SORRY IF I GAVE YOU
A WEDGIE.
LET GO OF HIM!
LET GO, KARI,
OR HE'LL GET YOU, TOO!
NO. I WON'T
LET YOU GO, T.K.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU TWO
ARE FALLING FOR EACH OTHER!
Together: AAH!
T.K.! KARI!
HA HA HA!
AAH!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ Thinking ] I'M SORRY
I LET YOU DOWN, MATT.
WAIT A SECOND.
MATT!
WHAT WOULD HE SAY?
Matt's voice:
T.K., DON'T EVER GIVE UP.
T.K.: [ Thinking ] MATT?
T.K., I HAVE FAITH IN YOU,
BUT IT WON'T HELP IF YOU
DON'T HAVE FAITH IN YOURSELF.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
YOU HAVE TO FIGHT
TO THE VERY END.
I PROMISE YOU, MATT,
I'LL NEVER GIVE UP THE FIGHT.
AAH!
IF I DON'T DO IT,
THIS WORLD AND OUR WORLD
WILL BE DESTROYED.
I HAVE TO DO IT FOR MATT,
FOR ANGEMON, FOR EVERYBODY!
T.K.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE
THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE
THE CHAMPIONS ♪
ANGEMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
WARP DIGEVOLVE.
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE
THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE
THE CHAMPIONS ♪
MAGNA ANGEMON.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON, HEY, DIGIMON ♪
ANGEMON, I KNEW
YOU COULD DIGEVOLVE!
♪ HEY, DIGIMON, HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ THE CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
HA HA HA!
I AM MAGNA ANGEMON.
I HAVE EIGHT SHINING WINGS
AND A BEAM SHIELD.
I WIELD THE MIGHTY SWORD
EXCALIBUR,
AND MY DEVASTATING ATTACK
IS THE GATE OF DESTINY.
CHEW ON THIS.
I'M NOT HUNGRY.
♪ CHAMPIONS ♪
I GUESS MY SWORD
TRUMPS YOURS.
AAH!
NOW TO BRING OUR FRIENDS
BACK TO NORMAL.
MAGNA ANTIDOTE!
Together: HUH?
Tai: WOW,
WHAT A WEIRD DREAM.
I HAD AN INCREDIBLE URGE
TO CARRY SOME KEYS.
KARI! T.K.!
HA HA!
GREAT JOB.
IF IT WASN'T
FOR YOUR ADVICE,
I DON'T THINK
I WOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE.
HUH?
WHEN DID ANGEMON DIGEVOLVE?
YOU LOOK GREAT!
TURN AROUND. LET ME SEE.
VERY WELL.
SO THE DIGIDESTINED THINK
THE DARK MASTERS
ARE ALL THAT
EASILY DEFEATED, HMM?
WELL, GUESS AGAIN.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONES
WITH AN ARMY OF FRIENDS.
TA-DA!
THIS IS MORE FUN
THAN A BARREL OF FLYING MONKEYS!
DIGIDESTINED,
MEET THE VILEOMON.
THEIR NIGHTMARE SHOCK
WILL GIVE YOU A RUDE AWAKENING!
Matt: WE'RE SURROUNDED!
Sora: OH, NO!
WE CAN'T ESCAPE!
T.K.: COME ON,
TOUGHEN UP.
I'M WITH YOU, T.K.
OUR ONLY CHANCE
IS IF WE COMBINE OUR POWERS,
BUT THE PROBLEM IS,
WE'RE STILL MISSING
SOME OF OUR FRIENDS.
WAIT FOR ME.
SORRY WE'RE LATE.
Sora: IT'S MIMI!
ARE WE TOO LATE?
Voice: PUMMEL WAH!
I SLICED. I GUESS
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
WORK ON MY SWING, HUH?
ALL RIGHT, GANG, GIVE THEM
THE FULL DIGIMON ATTACK.
SUPER THUNDER STRIKE!
HORN BLASTER!
AAH!
Together: NICE SHOT!
[ SCREECHING ]
PUMMEL WAH!
AAH!
[ SHRIEKING ]
UH-OH!
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
GOMAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
DIGEVOLVE INTO CHAMPION.
IKKAKUMON!
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
IKKAKUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
DIGEVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE.
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
ZUDOMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
TENTOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
KABUTERIMON!
KABUTERIMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
DIGEVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE.
MEGAKABUTERIMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
VULCAN'S HAMMER!
AAH!
MOST IMPRESSIVE.
TRUMP SWORD!
HORN BUSTER!
Together: YAY!
FLOWER CANNON!
AAH!
CELESTIAL ARROW!
WINGED BLADE!
AAH!
GATE OF DESTINY!
[ SCREAMING ]
Together: WOW!
OHH. HUH?
Together: HEY, REMEMBER US?
TERRA FORCE!
GIGA MISSILE!
AAH!
[ GASPING ]
Matt: THE LAST REMNANTS
OF SPIRAL MOUNTAIN
ARE DISAPPEARING.
THE DARK MASTERS' CONTROL
OVER THE DIGITAL WORLD
IS FINALLY GONE.
GOOD RIDDANCE!
All: BYE!
Voice: TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
Voice #2: GOODBYE!
YOU KNOW, WE HAVE
STRANGE-LOOKING FRIENDS.
THEY MIGHT NOT HAVE
THE BEST FASHION SENSE,
BUT THEY'RE THE BEST FRIENDS
WE'VE EVER HAD.
Izzy: HMM. WE HAVE
E-MAIL FROM GENNAI.
Sora: WHAT'S IT SAY?
NOT NOW. I NEED A NAP.
IT'S COMING IN NOW.
IS HE CONGRATULATING US?
GENNAI SAYS THE DARK MASTERS
AREN'T THE REAL ENEMIES.
HUH?
IT SAYS THE REAL ENEMY
IS AN EVIL FORCE
WHOSE VERY EXISTENCE
WARPS THE DIGIWORLD
AND CREATED
THE DARK MASTERS.
I DON'T THINK WE'RE
OUT OF THE WOODS QUITE YET.
WAIT. IF IT'S NOT
THE DARK MASTERS,
THEN WHO DO WE
FIGHT NEXT? AAH!
Together: WHAT? AAH!
Mimi: WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT IS THE EVIL FORCE
THAT GENNAI WAS WARNING
THE DIGIDESTINED ABOUT?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS."