Tai: SO THERE WE WERE,
FALLING LIKE CRAZY.
THAT'S WHEN GOMAMON TELLS
ALL THE FISH IN THE RIVER
TO SWIM CLOSE TOGETHER
AND MAKE A BOAT FOR US.
LATER WE FIND A BEACH
WITH A WHOLE BUNCH
OF THESE PHONE BOOTHS.
WE TRIED CALLING HOME, BUT
NONE OF THEM SEEMED TO WORK.
NEXT, WE GOT TOTALLY
THRASHED ON BY SHELLMON.
HE SPRAYED SEA WATER
LIKE A FIRE HOSE.
MY BUD AGUMON
GOT STEPPED ON,
AND THAT MADE HIM MAD.
HE DIGIVOLVED INTO GREYMON
AND GAVE SHELLMON A RIDE
HE WON'T FORGET,
THEN HE TURNED BACK
INTO AGUMON.
DUDES, THIS PLACE IS WILD!
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
FOX KIDS WORLDWIDE AND
THE U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGI ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE
THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
Tai: WE'VE ALMOST
SEARCHED THE WHOLE ISLAND,
AND WE STILL HAVEN'T
FOUND ANY PEOPLE,
JUST SOME MONSTERS
WITH ATTITUDE.
BUT THEY COULDN'T
BEAT OUR DIGIMON FRIENDS,
WHO CAN TURN INTO
THESE AWESOME FIGHTERS,
LIKE WHEN AGUMON
DIGIVOLVED INTO GREYMON
AND KICKED SHELLMON
TO THE CURB.
HE WAS SO COOL.
YO, AGUMON!
WHAT'S UP, TAI?
I LIKE IT WHEN
YOU'RE GREYMON.
NO OFFENSE, BUT WHY DON'T
YOU JUST STAY THAT WAY?
I CAN'T.
HUMPH!
BUT EVEN SUPERHEROES
NEED A REST.
AH! OOGAH!
HA HA HA!
HUH?
RAWWRR!
WHO'S THAT DIGIMON?
IT'S A MONOCHROMON.
BUT DON'T WORRY
ABOUT HIM.
HE'S A LAID-BACK
DIGIMON.
RAWWRR!
Tentomon: ALTHOUGH IT
IS WISE TO BE A BIT CAUTIOUS
WITH THE MONOCHROMON,
THEY DO TEND TO GET A BIT
MIFFED WHEN THEY'RE HUNGRY.
Tai: THEN HE
MUST BE STARVING
'CAUSE HE
LOOKS REALLY MAD.
Mimi: AND I THINK
HE WANTS TO EAT US!
RAWWRR!
HUH!
HUH!HUH!
THERE ARE 2 OF THEM!
WE'RE CAUGHT BETWEEN A ROCK
AND 2 SETS OF TEETH!
RAWWRR!
WE'RE CAUGHT BETWEEN A ROCK
AND 2 SETS OF TEETH!
AAH!
RUN!
Tai: SOMETHING MUST HAVE
SET THOSE MONOCHROMON OFF.
Tentomon: THEY'RE
FIGHTING OVER TERRITORY.
THEY CAN JUST
HAVE IT, THEN.
HEY!
PARUMON, DON'T LEAVE
WITHOUT ME!
THEY DEFINITELY DON'T
NEED US HANGIN' AROUND.
RAWWRR!
OUCH!
T.K., COME ON!
BETTER HURRY UP, YOU GUYS!
OK, WE'RE COMING!
RAWWRR!
[SPLASH]
Mimi: I DON'T WALK
THIS MUCH UNLESS
I'M AT A MALL,
AND AS YOU CAN SEE,
WE'RE NOWHERE
NEAR ONE.
MIMI, STOP WHINING.
NO! MY FEET HURT!
MAYBE IF YOU'D TAKE OFF
YOUR BOOTS AND SOCKS,
YOU'D FEEL BETTER, MIMI.
IT'S MUCH MORE
PRACTICAL, I THINK.
I'M NOT WALKING IN DIRT
IN MY BARE FEET!
I LOVE THE FEEL
OF DIRT UNDER MY FEET,
ESPECIALLY
BETWEEN MY TOES.
Mimi: GROSS!
Chip: IT APPEARS THAT WE MAY
BE LOSING OUR LIGHT SOURCE.
Sora: WHAT
A WEIRD SUNSET.
THIS WHOLE ISLAND
IS WEIRD,
AND WHO KNOWS WHAT
WILL COME OUT AT NIGHT?
WAIT! I DETECT WATER!
STAY HERE
WHILE I CHECK IT OUT.
YES, AS USUAL, I'M RIGHT!
IT'S A LAKE
WITH FRESH, CLEAN WATER,
AND A VARIETY OF TASTY FISH.
IT'S A PERFECT CAMPSITE.
MAYBE I CAN FINALLY SOAK
MY POOR ACHY FEET.
YAY! WE GET TO SWIM!
GOMAMON, YOU BETTER
WAIT AND MAKE SURE
IT'S SAFE FIRST!
THAT'S WHY I THINK
WE SHOULD KEEP WALKING
AND STOP
ALL THE COMPLAINING.
EVERYBODY'S HUNGRY.
WE HAVE TO
FIND SOME FOOD.
THAT IS A GOOD PLAN.
I LIKE THAT PLAN A LOT.
Piyomon: IT SHOULD BE SAFE
TO REST HERE TONIGHT.
Sora: YEAH. I LOVE
CAMPING OUTSIDE.
IF I WON'T WALK IN DIRT,
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'LL SLEEP IN IT?
MIMI, DO YOU
SEE A HOTEL HERE?
[GASP]
WHA?
Tai: WHAT'S THAT?
T.K.: IT LOOKS
LIKE A TROLLEY CAR.
Chip: THAT'S ODD.
THE LIGHTS JUST CAME ON.
MAYBE THERE ARE SOME
REAL PEOPLE IN THERE.
LET'S CHECK IT OUT!
Mimi: MAYBE THEY CAN
TAKE US BACK HOME
IN AIR-CONDITIONED COMFORT!
MIMI, WAIT UP!
BUMMER! IT'S EMPTY!
TOTALLY EMPTY.
NO TROLLEY CAR'S
THIS CLEAN.
OH, GOODY!
THESE CUSHIONS ARE COMFY.
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
REMEMBER THOSE
WEIRD PHONE BOOTHS
WE SAW ON THE BEACH?
SOMETHING
JUST AS FREAKY
COULD HAPPEN HERE.
YEAH, LIKE
THIS SUDDENLY MOVING
ALL BY ITSELF.
POSSIBLY, BUT THEN AGAIN,
MAYBE THAT'S HOW WE'RE
GOING TO GET HOME.
SO WE HAVE NOTHING
TO LOSE BY STAYING HERE.
OH, CAN WE EAT NOW?
THAT'S RIGHT. I FORGOT.
Chip: GOMAMON,
STOP PLAYING IN THE WATER!
I CAN'T CATCH ANY FISH
IF YOU KEEP ON
WARNING THEM AWAY!
YUM! YUM!
YOU CAN'T GET TOO MANY
BERRIES DOWN THE HATCH.
MMM...
POW!
OH!
HA HA HA! OH, BOY,
YOU BETTER WATCH
THAT KILLER BREATH
OF YOURS, PATAMON.
UGH!
THOSE ARE BAD MUSHROOMS.
YOU SHOULDN'T PICK 'EM.
THEY'LL MAKE YOU SICK.
OH!
I'D BE A BIG MESS
WITHOUT YOU, PARUMON.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
OH, STOP!
Matt: WE'RE ALL SET
TO COOK DINNER.
NOW ALL WE NEED
IS THE GRUB.
GREAT, BUT HOW
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO
LIGHT THE FIRE?
LIKE THIS.
HA!
WOW, AGUMON, YOU'RE THE MAN!
AWE.
HEY, LOOKIT!
WE CAUGHT A BUNCH OF FISH!
AWESOME, IZZY.
LET'S EAT 'EM.
THANKS, SQUIRT.
HA HA!
THIS IS WHERE I WISH WE
HAD A MICROWAVE. HUH?!
ME, TOO, BECAUSE
YOU'RE ABOUT TO
LOSE YOUR FINGERS.
WHY DON'T YOU
USE A STICK?
HOW DID YOU COME UP
WITH THAT, MATT?
BECAUSE I'M THE MAN!
THIS IS
SURPRISINGLY GOOD!
MMM! MMM!
DELICIOUS!
T.K.: MATT, MOM ONLY
LETS ME EAT FISH STICKS.
I WON'T TELL.
I NEVER EAT
WITH MY FINGERS.
T.K., IT'S ALL RIGHT!
YEAH. YOU'RE HANGIN'
WITH THE BIG BOYS NOW.
OK. MMM...RRRR...
HEY, SORA?
WHAT?
MATT DOESN'T TREAT T.K.
LIKE A BROTHER,
ONLY LIKE HE'S A BOTHER.
IS IT JUST ME, OR HAVE
YOU NOTICED THAT, TOO?
YEAH.
I WONDER--
MATT'S STILL LEARNING
TO BE A BIG BROTHER.
MAYBE.
[YAWN]
HEY, JOE,
WATCHA LOOKIN' AT?
I'M TRYIN' TO FIGURE OUT
WHICH DIRECTION
WE'VE BEEN GOING,
BUT THE STARS SEEM
TO BE ALL MIXED UP.
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO FIND
THE NORTH STAR ANYWHERE.
Sora: I KNOW.
I DON'T RECOGNIZE
ANY OF THESE CONSTELLATIONS.
Tai:
YOU'RE FORGETTING
YOUR ASTRONOMY.
IF YOU CAN'T
SEE THE NORTH STAR,
THEN IT MUST BE
ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE WORLD.
DO YOU THINK WE COULD BE
IN THE SOUTHERN HEMISPHERE?
YES, I GUESS
IT'S POSSIBLE.
THAT IS IF WE'RE
STILL ON EARTH.
WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
[YAWN]
LOOK. PATAMON'S TIRED.
HMMM...
[SNORING]
I'M GETTING
REALLY TIRED MYSELF.
WAIT A SECOND.
I THINK WE SHOULD TAKE
TURNS STANDING GUARD.
ALL RIGHT, WHO
WANTS TO GO FIRST?
HOW ABOUT IF EACH
OF US STANDS GUARD
FOR ABOUT AN HOUR?
NOT T.K.!
AWE, COME ON.
ME, TOO, MATT!
NO! YOU'RE TOO YOUNG,
AND YOU NEED YOUR REST!
I'M GETTING COLD.
I NEED
A WARM BLANKET
TO HELP ME SLEEP.
HEY, GABUMON,
MIMI MIGHT SNEAK UP
ON YOU AND STEAL YOUR FUR.
SO IF YOU FEEL
A LITTLE TUG,
IT MIGHT BE HER
ABOUT TO CUT--
TAI, THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
STOP TAI!
QUIT IT!
WHAT ARE YOU
BUGGIN' ABOUT?
GABUMON
TOLD YOU TO STOP,
SO KNOCK IT OFF!
HEY, YOU CAN'T TELL ME
WHAT TO DO.
T.K.: YOU GUYS,
STOP FIGHTING!
HUH?
YOU'D BOTH MAKE
GREAT GUARDS.
WHO GOES FIRST?
I WILL.
I'M NEXT!
AHH...
[YAWN]
HOW ABOUT IF IZZY
TAKES OVER AFTER THAT,
AND THEN I
FINISH UP THE NIGHT?
I PROPOSE THAT THE REST
OF US TREK BACK TO THE BUS
AND GET SOME SHUT-EYE.
Mimi: I CAN'T SLEEP
WITH ALL OF YOU HERE.
QUIT COMPLAINING.
SO IT'S NOT PERFECT.
JUST BE GLAD WE HAVE
A PLACE TO SLEEP.
THAT'S RIGHT, MIMI!
Joe: GOOD NIGHT.
DON'T LET
THE MONOCHROMON BITE.
[THINKING] THANKS FOR
REMINDING ME, T.K.
[THINKING]
MY FEET STILL HURT.
[THINKING] WHY
IS THERE A TROLLEY HERE?
MAYBE IT'S THE ALIENS.
MAYBE THEY KNEW WE
NEEDED IT.
[THINKING] I HOPE I DON'T
GET ANY MONSTER COOTIES.
AHH...
GABUMON?
YEAH?
GO OVER AND LAY DOWN
WITH MY BROTHER.
WHY, MATT?
BECAUSE YOUR FUR'S
MAKING ME SWEAT.
NOW, GO!
BECAUSE YOU WANT ME
TO KEEP T.K. WARM.
HEY, I DIDN'T SAY THAT!
YOU JUST DON'T
WANT TO ADMIT IT.
WHATEVER.
AHH...
THANKS, MATT.
[GASP]
AHH...
[YAWN]
TAI, YOU DON'T
WANNA FALL ASLEEP
ON YOUR FIRST NIGHT WATCH.
MY EYES WON'T STAY OPEN.
I'M GOIN' TO THE LAKE
AND SPLASH SOME WATER
ON MY FACE.
HUH?!
WHO'S THERE?
OH, MATT.
DON'T YOU THINK
I CAN HANDLE THIS?
I COULDN'T SLEEP.
OH? AND WHY NOT?
LOOK, I'M SORRY
ABOUT EARLIER.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO GET SO MAD.
IT'S JUST BEING HERE
AND HAVING TO WATCH T.K.
DO YOU GUYS EVEN LIVE
IN THE SAME HOUSE?
NOT ANYMORE.
WE'RE HALF-BROTHERS
AND WE DON'T GET TO
SEE EACH OTHER MUCH.
WELL, THAT
EXPLAINS A LOT.
OH!
HUH?
MATT'S A LITTLE STRANGE.
[HARMONICA PLAYS]
WHA?
[HARMONICA PLAYING
CONTINUES]
WHAT A WONDERFUL SOUND.
♪
MAYBE TO A SAINT BERNARD
WITH A HORN
ON HIS FOREHEAD.
[HARMONICA PLAYS]
HMM.
♪
AHH...
HUH?
AH!
WATCH OUT
FOR THE FIRE SPARKS!
[RUMBLING]
WHOA!
HEY!
AAH!
OH, NO!
RAWWRR!
AAH!
WHAT'S THAT HORRIBLE SOUND?
IT'S AN EARTHQUAKE!
THE TROLLEY'S
STARTING TO MOVE,
AND I DON'T THINK
IT'S TAKING US HOME!
IT'S TAKING US
TOWARD THAT SEADRAMON.
OH, NO! SEADRAMON!
RAWWRR!
WE'RE GONNA
GET EATEN FOR SURE!
RAWWRR!
THE LAND'S MOVING!
Agumon: HOLD ON!
WE'RE GOING
FOR A RIDE!
Tai: IT'S LIKE WE'RE
ON A MONSTER LONG BOARD.
HE'S PULLING US ALONG
BY HIS TAIL.
I DON'T THINK HE EVEN
REALIZES WE'RE HERE.
Tentomon: PERHAPS NOT.
HE'S A BIT DENSE.
AS LONG AS HE DOESN'T
SEE US, WE SHOULD BE SAFE.
DON'T BE TOO SURE.
YOU GUYS JINXED US!
NOW HE KNOWS WE'RE HERE!
Agumon & Tai: WHAT?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING?
Chip: I GUESS
HE DOES KNOW WE'RE HERE!
THAT BIG RED THING
WAS HIS TAIL!
RAWWRR!
IT WASN'T MY FAULT.
WHOA!
RAWWRR!
HE'S COMIN' BACK,
AND HE'S NOT HAPPY!
Joe: WE'RE GONNA CRASH
INTO THE SHORE!
Mimi: THIS IS REALLY
GONNA MESS UP MY HAIR!
T.K.!
MATT, I'M
JUST LETTING YOU KNOW
MY FUR'S GONNA GET WET
AND I'M GONNA STINK!
YUH-OH!
AAH!
AAH!AAH!
Tai: GREAT. HE LEFT US RIGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE LAKE!
Chip: I DON'T SUPPOSE
WE COULD TRICK HIM
INTO TAKING US BACK.
RAWWRR!
Tai: GET READY! HE'S ATTACKING!
Agumon: COME ON, YOU GUYS.
LET'S SEND HIM BACK
TO THE FISHIES!
Gabumon: NO PROBLEM!
SPIRAL TWISTER!
POW!
POISON IVY!
RAWWRR...
SUPER SHOCKER!
RAWWRR!
PEPPER BREATH!
Echo: BREATH...
BREATH.
RAWWRR!
AGUMON, DIGIVOLVE!
I'VE BEEN TRYIN',
BUT I CAN'T SEEM TO
DO IT THIS TIME, TAI.
YOU HAVE TO!
MAYBE MY BODY
HASN'T RECOVERED
FROM THE LAST BITE.
BUT IF YOU CAN'T HELP US,
HOW ARE WE GONNA STOP
SEADRAMON?
Matt: T.K.,
OVER HERE!
MATT!
MATT, BE CAREFUL
OR THE MONSTER
WILL GET YA--AAH!
T.K.!
GOMAMON, GO!
HURRY UP, MATT!
GET OUT FAST!
IT'S SEADRAMON! HE'S BACK!
GOMAMON, YOU CAN DO IT!
RIGHT!
HEY!
OVER HERE, YOU
OVERGROWN WATER LIZARD!
HISS!
HOWLING BLASTER! HAAA!
WHOA!
I HATE THIS!
IT'S ALL
MY FAULT.
MATT WAS
ONLY TRYING TO
SAVE ME.
I'LL NEVER
FORGIVE MYSELF.
NO!
WAA-AAAH!
THIS IS NOT GOOD!
SEADRAMON MAY
BE A BUBBLE BRAIN,
BUT ONCE HE FINDS HIS PREY,
HE WON'T LET GO.
MATT, HANG ON!
ARRRR!
PATAMON, PLEASE HELP HIM!
HIT HIM WITH A BUBBLE BOOM.
SEADRAMON'S
WAY TOO BIG.
I JUST DON'T
HAVE ENOUGH POWER NOW.
GABUMON, YOU'RE STRONGER.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
ALL RIGHT.
MATT IS IN TROUBLE,
AND I MUST HELP.
Matt: GABUMON!
T.K.: DON'T GIVE UP!
I'LL FIND A WAY TO SAVE YOU
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO!
MATT, HOLD ON!
RAWWRR!
Gabumon, thinking:
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
ANY OF THIS,
BUT I HAVE TO SAVE MATT.
WHAT'S A LITTLE
STINKY FUR COMPARED
TO A FRIEND LIKE HIM?
[FANFARE]
Gabumon: MA-A-A-AT!
GABUMON!
AH!
Gabumon: GABUMON...
DIGIVOLVE TO...
GARURUMON!
GRRR-RAH!
UNH!
OH! AH!
GRRRR!
WHA-AH-AH!
[PANTING]
ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT, MATT?
YEAH, BUT WHERE'S
GABUMON?
HISS...
RAH!
RAWWRR!
Tentomon: GARURUMON'S FUR
IS LEGENDARY.
IT'S STRONG AS STEEL.
HE'S LIKE
A GROWLING TORPEDO!
THAT'S ASTONISHING,
THEN HE MUST BE INVINCIBLE!
WELL, THAT'S WHAT
I'VE HEARD, ANYWAY.
WE'LL SOON FIND OUT.
I HOPE YOU'RE
NOT EXAGGERATING,
TENTOMON,
WITH ANOTHER ONE OF
YOUR WILD FISH TALES
AGAIN.
HE COULD BE.
BUT I HEARD ABOUT IT.
RAWWRR!
Tentomon: WHOA! SEADRAMON'S
USING HIS LETHAL ICE BLAST!
HOWLING BLASTER!
RAH!
ARRR...RARR...
AAH!
HA HA!
RAWWRR!
Matt: GABUMON!
FLYING'S SURE A GOOD WAY
TO KEEP MY FUR DRY.
YOU DIGIVOLVED INTO
GARURUMON JUST IN TIME!
AW, GABUMON, THANKS
FOR SAVING MY BROTHER!
ANYTIME, LITTLE FRIEND.
MATT, YOU WERE SO AWESOME
AGAINST THAT MONSTER.
YA THINK SO?
YOU KNOW,
YOU WERE THE MAN!
AND YOU'RE
THE WOLF MAN!
HA HA HA!
OK, VERY FUNNY. BUT HOW
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO GET BACK?
JUST WATCH!
FISH POWER!
Mimi: GABUMON, MAY I
USE YOU FOR A PILLOW?
I PROMISE
I WON'T TAKE YOUR FUR.
ACTUALLY, THERE SEEMS
TO BE A PATTERN HERE.
THIS TIME ONLY GABUMON
COULD DIGIVOLVE.
YEAH, IZZY'S RIGHT.
AGUMON
WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO COULD
DO IT BEFORE.
HMM...
AAH!
HANG ON!
CAN'T...BREATHE!
UGH! UNH!
GREYMON!
GET ME OUTTA HERE!
GRRR!
RAH!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S ALL BEGINNING
TO MAKE SENSE.
AGUMON DIGIVOLVED
WHEN I WAS IN DANGER.
THAT HAS TO BE THE ANSWER.
OUR DIGIMON DIGIVOLVES
WHEN WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
WHOA, THAT MUST BE IT.
[SNORING]
HEY, WATCH IT.
IS IT TIME TO
GO TO THE MALL?
WE'VE BEEN HERE ONE DAY,
AND I THINK SHE'S PUT
SOME MUSCLE ON HER.
YEAH. MAYBE IF
SHE PUTS IN SOME EFFORT,
SHE'LL BECOME
A HARD-BODIED MACHINE
LIKE I AM.
I HOPE SHE
GROWS PINK WINGS
JUST LIKE MY WINGS.
YOU MUST BE KIDDING. HMMM...
[SNORING]
AHH...
[SNORING AND SIGHING]
[YAWN]
HUH?
[HARMONICA PLAYS]
[PLAYING HARMONICA]
♪
AHH...BIG BRO,
YOU'RE THE BEST.
♪
AHHH...