A STRANGE BEING
NAMED GENNAI ASKED US TO
COME TO HIS CONTINENT
TO DEFEAT HIS ENEMIES.
HE TOLD US WE HAVE THE POWER
TO DIGIVOLVE EVEN MORE,
BUT NOT WITHOUT SPECIAL TAGS
AND CRESTS THAT WERE HIDDEN
BY DEVOMON.
WE BUILT A RAFT, WITH THE HELP
OF SOME ISLAND DIGIMON,
AND T.K.'S DIGIEGG HATCHED
INTO POYOMON.
WHILE ON THE RAFT,
WE MET WHAMON, AND
WERE SWALLOWED BY HIM.
HE TOOK US TO AN UNDERWATER
STORE WHERE WE FOUND THE TAGS.
NOW ALL WE NEEDED
WERE THE CRESTS.
BUT WHERE TO LOOK NEXT?
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
FOX KIDS WORLDWIDE AND
THE U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGI ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE
THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
WE LEFT FILE ISLAND
ALMOST 5 DAYS AGO.
Whamon: WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
HUH?
HEY, I THINK
I SEE AN ICEBERG!
EITHER THAT, OR IT COULD BE
THE CONTINENT OF SERVER.
IT'S SERVER.
ALL RIGHT!
ALL RIGHT EVERYBODY,
WAKE UP! RISE AND SHINE!
WE'RE LANDING AT SERVER!
I WAS ONLY RESTING MY EYES.
WELL, YOUR EYES WERE
SNORING PRETTY LOUDLY.
COME ON, WE'RE GONNA
BE THERE IN A FEW MINUTES!
GOTTA MAKE SURE WE HAVE
EVERYTHING WE NEED!
Sora:
WE'RE REALLY THERE?
Izzy: WELL, I'M READY
FOR LAND AGAIN!
T.K.: I'D SURE LIKE A BED
THAT DIDN'T MOVE!
Agumon: WOW, THAT ISLAND
IS HUGE!
Biyomon: I'VE NEVER SEEN
AN ISLAND SO BIG!
Tentomon: IT'S NOT AN ISLAND,
IT'S THE CONTINENT OF SERVER.
MIMI, YOU'VE JUST
GOTTA WAKE UP AND
LOOK AT THIS!
WE'RE GOING TO
LAND ON A
BIG CONTINENT!
NO, I'M GETTING
A PEDICURE...
AW, MIMI.
[LAUGHTER]
ALMOST THERE!
SERVER, HERE WE COME!
WHOAH!
[LAUGHTER]
Sora: COME ON, MIMI!
UH, THIS IS A LITTLE TOO
EXTREME SPORTS FOR ME.
IS THERE SOME WAY
I CAN BE AIRLIFTED
ONTO THE ISLAND?
SORRY WE CAN'T JUST MOVE
THE CONTINENT FOR YOU, MIMI.
ACCORDING TO THE MAP, THIS IS
THE BEST BEACH TO COME ASHORE.
JUST PUT ONE FOOT
IN FRONT OF THE OTHER,
AND YOU'LL BE FINE!
IT'S AS EASY
AS FALLING OFF A LOG!
YEAH? I'VE FALLEN OFF PLENTY
OF LOGS, AND BELIEVE ME, IT'S
NOT AS EASY AS IT--AHH!
UGH!
I THINK I BROKE A NAIL!
Whamon: GOOD LUCK
FINDING THE CRESTS!
All: GOOD-BYE, WHAMON! SO LONG!
All: GOOD-BYE, WHAMON!
SO, WHAT ARE WE
GOING TO DO, NOW?
WHILE YOU WERE ASLEEP,
WHAMON TOLD US WHERE TO GO.
IN THE FOREST,
A FEW MILES FROM HERE,
THERE'S A KOROMON VILLAGE.
KOROMON. WHY, THAT
SOMEHOW SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
I WAS A KOROMON
THE DAY YOU GOT HERE!
I FORGOT!
Tentomon: THE KOROMON
ARE A GROUP OF DIGIMON,
ALWAYS WILLING TO
HELP OUT THOSE IN NEED.
OK, GANG,
LET'S MOVE OUT!
All: YEAH! YOU BETCHA!
Sora: THIS PLACE IS BIGGER
THAN I THOUGHT.
Gomamon:
IT'S SIMPLE PHYSICS.
THE UNIVERSE IS EXPANDING.
I THINK MY FEET
ARE EXPANDING.
WE'VE BEEN WALKING
ALL DAY LONG,
AND THERE'S NO SIGN
OF THE VILLAGE YET!
OH, I'D GIVE ANYTHING
TO BE IN A BATHTUB
WITH LOTS OF BUBBLE
BATH IN IT!
YOU CAN DO THAT
ONCE WE GET
TO THE VILLAGE.
YOU HONESTLY THINK THEY
HAVE BATHTUBS, PALMON?
WELL...
HMMM? [SNIFFS]
AGUMON, WHAT IS IT?
TAI, I SMELL KOROMON
OVER IN THIS DIRECTION.
REALLY?
A FOREST!
All: A FOREST!?
Matt: IS THAT WHERE
THE KOROMON VILLAGE IS?
IT MUST BE!
COME ON!
Sora: TAI, WAIT A MINUTE!
TAI!
Tai: ALMOST THERE!
All: AHH! WOW!
T.K.:
GREAT! PUP TENTS.
WE CAN REST!
EVEN BETTER, A BATH!
WAIT, STOP!
UHH...
TAI: AGUMON, WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
SOMETHING DOESN'T
FEEL RIGHT.
All: UH-OH!
A BATH!
SOMEBODY GRAB ME
A RUBBER DUCK!
EXCUSE ME,
WHERE'S THE SHAMPOO?
HMMM?
PALMON, DO YOU REALLY
THINK THESE ARE KOROMON?
NO WAY, MIMI,
THESE ARE PAGUMON.
[LAUGHTER]
Tentomon: PAGUMON. THERE ARE
MORE TO THEM THAN MEETS THE EYE.
OH!
OH, NO!
THEY'VE GOT MIMI!
DON'T LET 'EM GET AWAY!
AROUND THAT CORNER!
All: HUH?
TAI: WHICH WAY?
Mimi: OH, HELP!
TO THE TOWER!
MIMI!
HEY, LOOK UP THERE!
THAT'S MIMI'S HAT!
THERE'S THE PRICE TAG.
IT'S MIMI'S.
THAT'S MIMI'S PURSE. SHE NEVER
GOES ANYWHERE WITHOUT IT.
Izzy: LOGICALLY THAT CAN MEAN
ONLY ONE THING...SHE'S MISSING.
THAT'S IT!
HMM...
NO, TAI,
DON'T GO IN THERE!
MIMI!
♪ OH, WASH, WASH, WASH AWAY! ♪
UH...MIMI, SORRY!
AHH! HAVEN'T YOU TWO
EVER HEARD THE PHRASE
"KNOCK BEFORE ENTERING"?
MIMI, WE'RE HERE
TO RESCUE YOU!
OH! OW!
I BELIEVE I SAID
"DON'T GO IN."
AHHHHH...
♪ WELCOME TO OUR VILLAGE,
WE HOPE YOU NEVER GO ♪
♪ STAY AND VISIT HERE WITH US,
AND PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW ♪
THIS IS DEFINITELY
A PAGUMON VILLAGE.
SOMETHING'S WRONG
HERE, GABUMON.
I KNOW WHAT I SMELLED
WAS KOROMON.
I'D BET MY NOSE ON IT!
Pagumon: HERE'S YOUR
PU-PU PLATTER!
I FEEL LIKE A PRINCESS
IN A BEAUTIFUL PALACE!
I ONCE HAD
A CHIHUAHUA
NAMED PRINCESS.
HUH?
TAI, YOU DON'T SUPPOSE
THIS COULD BE A TRICK?
COURSE NOT. YOU THINK
I DON'T KNOW A GOOD
DIGIMON FROM A BAD ONE?
MM-MMM.
♪ WE CAN SHOW YOU SO MUCH FUN
IT WOULD BE INHUMANE! ♪
THIS IS REALLY STRANGE.
I ALWAYS HEARD
THE PAGUMON WERE
AWFUL PRANKSTERS.
YOU WERE JUST
HEARING AN AWFUL RUMOR.
Pagumon: NICE OF YOU
TO SAY THAT!
THESE GUYS ARE REALLY
NICE LITTLE DIGIMON!
Pagumon: RIGHT, NICE DIGIMON!
♪ NEXT TO YOU, WE'RE GENIUSES ♪
YOU LIKE THAT?
HUH?
Baby Poyo:
POYOMON DIGIVOLVE
INTO TOKOMON!
HEY, HE'S TOKOMON AGAIN!
THE FOOD MADE
HIM DIGIVOLVE.
CONGRATULATIONS!
[CRUEL LAUGHTER]
Tokomon: TOGETHER,
WE COULD MAKE ME
PATAMON AGAIN!
LET'S HEAR IT FOR TOKOMON!
All: WAY TO GO!
CONGRATULATIONS!
♪ CONGRATULATIONS, WAY TO GO,
WE'RE SO EXCITED, ALL AGLOW! ♪
[SNORING]
[EVIL CHUCKLE]
Tokomon: I WANT MY DIGIMOMMY!
WHAT'D I DO?
WHY ARE YOU PICKING ON ME?
BECAUSE YOU DIGIVOLVED!
YOU WERE SO
EASY TO FOOL!
WHAT A BUNCH
OF LOSERS! WOW!
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
All:
OH! GAZIMON!
Tokomon: LOOK, THOSE ARE
GAZIMON. ON THE EVIL SCALE
OF 1-10, 10 BEING BAD,
THESE DIGIMON ARE 12s!
AHHHHH!
WHERE DID THAT
TOKOMON COME FROM?
WELL, HE CAME TO OUR VILLAGE
WITH SOME HUMANS BUT--
THERE ARE HUMANS HERE?
Pagumons: YOU EAT TOO MUCH!
SIT STILL! STOP SQUIRMING!
AHHH!
YOU'RE NOT SO
SPECIAL NOW, ARE YA?
YEAH, YOU'RE NOT
SO SPECIAL NOW!
HUH?
First Gazimon:
ONE OF US HAS TO TELL
ETEMON
THAT DIGIDESTINED
HUMANS ARE HERE.
I'LL GO. I GOTTA
ASK HIM FOR TIME OFF
FOR A HARE-CUT, ANYWAY.
KEEP AN EYE
ON THOSE KIDS,
OR ETEMON WILL MAKE
DIGISTEW OUT OF YOU!
All: RIGHT!
[EVIL SNICKERS]
WHERE IS HE?
ETEMON, WHERE ARE YOU?
ETEMON!
WAIT TILL YOU HEAR
THE NEWS I HAVE FOR YOU.
WHERE ARE YOU, ETEMON?
ETEMON!
HAH.
HEY, WAIT!
WAIT! WHOA!
WHOA!
YEAH! THE CONCERT SENSATION
OF THE SERVER CONTINENT IS BACK!
ALL RIGHT!
IT'S ETEMON, THE KING!
Tentomon, VO: THERE IS NOTHING
ENTERTAINING ABOUT ETEMON.
HE HAS THE POWER TO CONTROL
ANYTHING ELECTRONIC THROUGH
HIS DARK NETWORK.
EVERYONE HAIL ETEMON,
THE TRUE KING!
NOW, SON, YOU'RE WAY TOO LOUD
FOR AN EARLY MORNING TIME
LIKE THIS. UNDERSTAND?
BUT YOU WERE THE ONE
USING THE AMPLIFIER, SIR.
NOW LET'S GET SOMETHING
STRAIGHT, SONNY BOY!
I'M THE MONARCH
OF ROCK 'N' ROLL.
YOUR JOB'S
TO MAKE ME HAPPY!
THE HUMANS
WILL BE HERE SOON!
YOU SEE, NOW, ONCE I START
MAKIN' MY FABULOUS MUSIC,
WELL, THOSE KIDS
ARE GONNA BE MINE.
THEY'LL JUST HAVE TO
COME OVER
AND SEE WHAT GREAT STAR'S
SINGIN' LIKE THAT!
THERE'S JUST
ONE THING WRONG.
HUH?
JUST THAT THOSE 7 KIDS
ARE ALREADY HERE.
THEY'VE BEEN AT
THE PAGUMON VILLAGE
SINCE YESTERDAY.
WHAT?! JUST WHAT
ARE YOU SAYIN'?
I HAD IT ALL
WORKED OUT, KID!
MY WHOLE PLAN'S FLAWLESS!
WELL, SOMEBODY FORGOT
TO TELL THOSE HUMANS.
NO! IT'S JUST NOT FAIR!
I AM THE KING HERE!
THEY GOTTA LEARN THE HARD WAY
WHAT YOU ALREADY KNOW--
THEY CAN'T BE MESSIN'
WITH THE ROYAL ONE!
I EXPECT MY PLANS
TO BE FOLLOWED. UH HUH!
HUH?
I ORDER YOU TO
LAUNCH THE DARK NETWORK!
LET'S GO!
WAIT FOR ME!
THIS WILL BE YOUR
GREATEST PERFORMANCE
YET, BOSS.
IT'S NOT EASY BEING
A SUPERSTAR,
LITTLE BUDDY,
BUT SOMEONE'S
GOTTA DO IT.
UH-HUH-HUH.
[MANIACAL LAUGHTER]
TOKOMON!
WHERE ARE YOU?
WHERE COULD HE
HAVE GONE TO?
TOKOMON, IF YOU CAN
HEAR ME, SAY SOMETHING!
LOOKS LIKE HE'S NOT
IN THE SOUTH PART.
HE'S NOT IN
THE VILLAGE.
CAN WE HURRY THIS UP?
I'M SCHEDULED FOR
A MUD PACK AND A FACIAL
IN HALF AN HOUR.
TOKOMON SHOULD
KNOW BETTER
THAN TO INTERRUPT YOUR
BEAUTY TREATMENTS.
YOU'RE SO RIGHT.
HUH? HE'S BEING
SARCASTIC.
WHAT?!
[COMMOTION]
WELL, HE'S NOT BY
THE WATERFALL.
OK. THANKS.
THIS IS BAD.
WHERE IS HE?
[SNICKERING]
Agumon: TOKOMON!
TOKOMON, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
SOMETHING IS DEFINITELY
WRONG HERE.
MY NOSE ALWAYS KNOWS!
I SMELL KOROMON.
IT'S COMING FROM
BEHIND THE WATERFALL!
WHAT?!
AGUMON!
TOKOMON!
HUH?
[WHIMPERING]
KOROMON!
BOY, YOU GUYS GOTTA
GET A BIGGER APARTMENT,
MAYBE SOMEPLACE WITH
A FEW MORE BEDROOMS.
THE PAGUMON CAME
AND LOCKED US IN
THESE CAGES!
ABOUT 3 DAYS AGO,
THEY CAME IN
AND TOOK OVER OUR
WHOLE VILLAGE.
THEN WE WERE REALLY RIGHT
AFTER ALL!
I APPRECIATE CHATTING
AS MUCH AS THE NEXT GUY,
BUT IF YOU UNTIE ME,
WE COULD GO WARN THE OTHERS.
RIGHT! I'LL HAVE YOU OUT
IN JUST A MINUTE.
I REALLY DON'T
THINK SO.
HMM? BUT YOU'RE GAZIMON!
EXACTLY RIGHT.
AND WE ARE GOING TO BE
GIVING THOSE HUMANS OF YOURS
TO KING ETEMON!
[EVIL CHUCKLE]
NO, YOU'RE NOT!
NOT QUITE!
WHY DON'T WE
TEACH THE LITTLE
LIZARD
A LESSON?
AGUMON!
TOKOMON'S REALLY
VERY SMALL.
HE CAN'T HAVE GONE
TOO FAR.
AGUMON'S BEEN GONE
A LONG TIME.
I WONDER IF HE'S
FOUND ANYTHING.
[GRUNTING]
Both: ELECTRIC STUN BLAST!
TWO AGAINST ONE
ISN'T FAIR!
GET UP, AGUMON!
TAI, PLEASE HELP ME
DIGIVOLVE.
GO AHEAD.
YELL IF YOU WANT.
HE CAN'T HEAR!
IF ONLY IT WEREN'T FOR
THIS WATERFALL!
WAIT! THAT'S IT!
[INHALES]
PEPPER BREATH!
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO DO, YOU DOLT?
PEPPER BREATH!
HUH? THAT'S WEIRD.
WHAT DO YOU SEE,
TAI?
SMOKE BY THE RIVER.
Joe: SMOKE? WHAT?
TK: IT'S TOKOMON!
NO, REALLY, IT'S NOTHING.
WE LOOKED BY THE RIVER
AND DIDN'T SEE A THING.
All: DIDN'T SEE A THING!
WELL, IT IS POSSIBLE
THAT TOKOMON ARRIVED
AFTER YOU PAGUMON
SEARCHED THE AREA.
HEY, I'LL CHECK IT OUT.
All: NO,
DON'T DO THAT!
HEY, SO WHAT'S
THE PROBLEM?
WE'RE JUST GOING TO
LOOK AROUND.
JUST TAKE OUR WORD
FOR IT.
Mimi: AAH!
EEW! EEW! EEW!
WHAT IS THIS THING?
Tentomon:
IT'S A BOTAMON!
WHY WOULD THERE
BE A BOTAMON
HERE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
BOTAMON IS THE SMALL
ACORN THAT DIGIVOLVES
INTO KOROMON
AND THEN INTO AGUMON.
THEN THE PAGUMON
LIED TO US.
All: ♪ IT'S TIME FOR US
TO LEAVE HERE ♪
♪ WE REALLY HATE TO GO ♪
♪ WE TOLD YOU
THIS WAS OUR PLACE ♪
♪ NOW YOU KNOW IT ISN'T SO ♪
♪ PAGUMON IS OUR NAME.
WE'RE CLEVER AND WE'RE BRIGHT ♪
♪ YOU CAN TELL THAT'S SO...♪
THERE THEY GO.
♪ BECAUSE WE'D RATHER RUN
THAN FIGHT! ♪
NEVER TRUST ANYTHING
WITHOUT FEET.
STOP IT!
GET READY,
LIZARD!
HERE'S A PRESENT
FOR YA!
TAI, WHERE ARE YOU?
AGUMON!
TAI! HELP ME!
HOLD ON, AGUMON!
HMM?
AGUMON, ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT?
NOW I AM.
SO, YOU'RE ONE
OF THE DIGIDESTINED!
DIGIVOLVING TIME.
AGUMON, GET UP!
YOU GOT IT!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
Agumon: AGUMON,
DIGIVOLVE TO...
GREYMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
OUTSTANDING!
SO, YOU LIKE TO FIGHT
2 AGAINST ONE, EH?
NOVA BLAST!
GREYMON DID IT!
TOKOMON! I THOUGHT
I'D LOST YOU AGAIN!
I'M LIKE A BOOMERANG.
I KEEP COMING BACK!
THE PAGUMON
ARE GONE.
YOU CAN ALL RETURN
TO YOUR VILLAGE
NOW.
All: THANK YOU!
Etemon:
WELL, HELLO!
OH, GREAT.
IT'S A DIGIELVIS.
YOU MEASLY LITTLE
DIGIDESTINED HUMANS,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
HELLO!
Koromon group:
IT'S ETEMON! OH, NO!
YOU MESSED UP ALL OF
MY BEAUTIFUL PLANS,
SO NOW I'M GONNA
HAVE TO PUNISH YOU
BY PLAYIN' A LITTLE NUMBER
YOU AIN'T GONNA LIKE.
I CALL IT DESTROYING
THE WHOLE VILLAGE!
DESTROY THE VILLAGE?
DO YOU THINK
HE CAN ACTUALLY
DO THAT?
DARK NETWORK,
CONCERT CRUSH!
EVERYONE,
DIGIVOLVE, NOW!
LET'S GO!
Gabumon: GABUMON,
DIGIVOLVE TO...
GARURUMON!
WELL, YA SAY YOU WANT
A DIGIVOLUTION?
GUESS WHAT?
THE ANSWER'S NO!
DARK NETWORK,
CONCERT CRUSH!
UH-HUH, UH-HUH!
HA HA HA HA!
DARK NETWORK,
YEAH, DARLIN'!
GOTCHA!
SOMETHING STRANGE
IS GOING ON!
DARK NETWORK! YEAH!
CONCERT CRUSH
TOOK OUR POWER!
Tentomon: DOES ROCK 'N' ROLL
HAVE THAT EFFECT
IN YOUR WORLD?
Sora: ONLY ON
OUR PARENTS.
SO THERE'S NO WAY FOR US
TO FIGHT THIS MONSTER?
Tentomon: AS WE ARE, NO.
IF ONLY WE COULD
DIGIVOLVE A STEP FURTHER--
Matt: A STEP FURTHER?
THAT MUST BE WHAT
GENNAI WAS REFERRING TO
WHEN HE TOLD US ABOUT
FINDING THE CRESTS
AND THE TAGS.
I THINK IT'S JUST
A LITTLE LATE FOR
THAT NOW, SORA.
HUH?
WHAT'S THIS?
THIS IS A SAFE PLACE
WHERE WE HIDE
WHEN ANYTHING BAD
HAPPENS TO OUR VILLAGE!
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
HUH?
I THINK I KNOW
WHAT THIS IS!
OK, WHAT?
A CREST.
A CREST?
EXACTLY! NOW WE'VE
GOT A CREST!
HOW AWESOME!
LOOK!
All: HUH?!
AH!
OH!
OOH!
Joe: DIDN'T THIS
USED TO BE A WALL?
Koromon:
YEAH, BUT THE CREST
MUST HAVE BROUGHT US
HERE.
THESE MOUNTAINS
ARE A LONG WAY
FROM OUR VILLAGE.
ALL RIGHT!
FREQUENT FLIER
MILES!
THIS PLACE IS THE BOMB!
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
HMM. WITH THIS CREST,
WE CAN DO ANYTHING WE WANT.
DO YOU KNOW, GUYS,
I THINK THIS IS
A FIRST STEP
ON A TRIP HOME!
UH, ETEMON, ABOUT
THE HUMAN CHILDREN--
YES, LITTLE BUDDY,
TRAPPING 'EM ALL
IN THAT CAVE
WAS MORE FUN THAN
LEARNIN' HOW TO
LIP SYNCH.
MAYBE NOT, BOSS.
THEY'RE MISSING.
HOW COULD YOU LOSE 'EM!
LEMME SEE!
THEY GOT AWAY!
THIS BUNCH IS A WHOLE LOT
MORE CLEVER THAN
I THOUGHT THEY WERE.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT THIS ONE.
THEN DEFEATING THOSE KIDS
IS GONNA EARN ME A STANDING
OVATION!
[EVIL CHORTLE]