WHEN I WENT FISHING,
I NEVER THOUGHT
I WOULD CATCH WHAT I DID.
OUR LITTLE GROUP
DECIDED TO EXPLORE
THE REST OF THIS ISLAND.
AND WHEN WE CAME UPON
WHAT LOOKED LIKE A CHURCH,
WELL, WE WERE MORE
THAN A LITTLE SURPRISED.
THE PEOPLE INSIDE LOOKED LIKE
THEY WERE CELEBRATING HALLOWEEN.
WE SHOULD'VE KNOWN THEY
WEREN'T ORDINARY PEOPLE.
AS IT TURNED OUT,
IT WAS THE BAKAMON HOLIDAY,
AND THESE PEOPLE WERE
ACTUALLY GHOSTS WHO WERE
PLANNING ON EATING US.
THANKFULLY, JOE FIGURED OUT
HOW TO TAKE AWAY
LORD BAKAMON'S POWER.
JUST ANOTHER DAY
IN PARADISE.
[SCREAMING]
T.K.: THIS IS TOTALLY
NO FAIR!
[BOTH SCREAM]
WHAT'S HAPPENING,
PATAMON?
T.K.:
WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
JUST WHEN
I THINK THIS PLACE
IS THE BOMB,
IT ALL GOES
CREEPY ON ME AGAIN.
SURE WOULD BE AWFUL
WITHOUT PATAMON.
YOU HAVE FAILED ME!
I'M SORRY, MASTER.
WE ALMOST HAD THEM,
DEVIMON,
AND THEN JUST WHEN--
[GAGGING]
NO, WAIT!
I CAN EXPLAIN!
Devimon: SPARE ME
YOUR PATHETIC EXCUSES.
Ogremon: YES, MASTER,
PLEASE, PLEASE,
JUST PUT ME DOWN!
AAH!
THANK YOU, MASTER.
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
UHH! UHH! UHH!
BOY, PATAMON,
I LIKE SWIMMING
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT THAT WATERFALL ALMOST
KNOCKED OFF MY UNDERPANTS.
Patamon: I THINK
MY WINGS SHRUNK.
THIS FITS.
WHOA. HMM.
LOOK AT ALL THAT WATER.
SOMEBODY MUST'VE LET
THE BATHTUB OVERFLOW.
I JUST HOPE
IT DIDN'T WASH OUT
OUR WAY OF FINDING
THE OTHERS.
T.K.: D-D-DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ME, PATAMON.
I'M NOT SCARED OF BEING
SEPARATED FROM THE OTHERS,
AND BEING LOST,
AND BEING HOMESICK.
YAHHH-AHH-AHH!
POOR LITTLE T.K.
I WISH I COULD HELP.
WHAT WOULD BIYOMON
DO IF SHE WERE HERE?
BIYOMON
DIGIVOLVE TO...
BIRDRAMON!
I WANT TO FLY HIGH
IN THE SKY, TOO,
BUT SOMEHOW, I CAN'T
SEEM TO DIGIVOLVE.
[CRYING]
HEY.
I WANNA FLY, TOO.
I WANNA DIGIVOLVE.
TO WHAT?
Patamon: HUH?
I MEAN, WHAT WILL
YOU DIGIVOLVE INTO?
DIDN'T THEY TELL YOU
AT DIGIMON SCHOOL,
OR SOMETHING?
OH. WELL, I WON'T
ACTUALLY KNOW
UNTIL
I DO DIGIVOLVE
AND FIND OUT
WHAT I AM.
WOW, SO IT'S A MYSTERY.
MAYBE YOU DIGIVOLVE
INTO SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
PORKYMON,
WITH SUPERSTRONG
OINK ATTACK,
AND THE POWER TO,
UM, OINK.
UH...MAYBE.
HMM. WELL,
HOW ABOUT HOGMON?
SUPERHOG SMELL
AND THE POWER
TO SNORT UP ENEMIES
IN A SINGLE SNIFF,
LIKE THIS.
I AM NOT A PIG, T.K.
IT'S OK TO BE A PIG.
I'M SURE IT IS,
ESPECIALLY FOR KIDS,
BUT THAT'S NOT ME.
[BELL RINGING,
TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
T.K.: HEY, I HEAR
A TRAIN COMIN'.
I BET YOU
WE CAN JUMP ON
AND RIDE THE CABOOSE
ALL THE WAY
BACK TO SUMMER CAMP.
Patamon: I THOUGHT
I FOUND SOMETHING.
T.K.: UM, MAYBE
IT'S AN INVISIBLE TRAIN.
DID A TRAIN GO BY?
IF IT DID,
IT'S THE MOST SILENT-EST,
MOST INVISIBLE-EST
TRAIN EVER.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
GO WHERE?
I'M NOT SURE,
BUT I GUESS WE'LL KNOW
WHEN WE GET THERE.
T.K.: WOW,
THIS IS THE BEST!
LET'S FIND
A SNACK BAR
AND GET SOME
COTTON CANDY.
PLACES LIKE THIS
ALWAYS HAVE
COTTON CANDY.
THEY MAKE CANDY
FROM COTTON?
OOH, I BET
THERE'S POPCORN
AND SNOW CONES
AND SOFT PRETZELS
AND ICE CREAM...
AND CANDY!
OH, BOY!
LET'S GO SEE!
LAST ONE THERE
IS A ROTTEN EGG!
[BOTH LAUGH]
HEY, CHECK THIS OUT.
WHOA!
[BOTH LAUGH]
WHEE!
AAH!
[SCREAMING AND LAUGHING]
Both: WHAT A SCREAM!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
THE STREETS FEEL
LIKE THEY'RE MADE
OUT OF MARSHMALLOWS.
Both: REAL SQUISHY!
HEY, YOU THINK IN AUTUMN
THOSE TOYS FALL
OFF THE TREES?
OOH.
MM-HMM.
[GIGGLING]
BUT WE CAN'T JUST
LIE HERE FOREVER,
CAN WE?
I GUESS WE'D BETTER
KEEP LOOKIN' AROUND.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I HEAR SOME STRANGE
NOISES OVER THERE.
HMM?
LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
HMM-HMM, HMM-HMM,
HMM-HMM.
T.K.: CRADLES.
LOTS OF 'EM.
WHAT NOW?
BOTAMON. IT'S
A BABY DIGIMON.
A BABY!
BO...BO...
T.K.: HE'S SO SOFT!
Patamon: THAT'S 'CAUSE
HE WAS JUST BORN.
WHAT ABOUT
THE OTHER ONES?
OHH!
OHH...
T.K.: WHAT'S
THIS ONE CALLED?
THAT'S PUNIMON.
PUNI! PUNI!
PUNY IS RIGHT.
HE'S MICRO-TINY.
HA HA!
HUH. WHAT'S
WITH THIS ONE?
LOOKS MORE
LIKE A GRANDPA
WITH A BIG BEARD.
OH, COME ON, NOW, T.K.
YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
THIS IS A LITTLE
BABY YURAMON.
HE'S LOOKIN'
RIGHT AT YOU.
AH-CHOO!
[BOTH GIGGLING]
AH.
HMM.
AH-CHOO!
HEY, PATAMON,
WHAT ARE THESE?
WHAT ARE WHAT?
OH.
THAT'S A DIGI-EGG.
HEY, NO WAY.
IT'S THE EGG
OF A DIGIMON.
I LIKE THE PRETTY PAINT,
BUT ARE YOU SAYIN'
THAT DIGIMON
HATCH OUT OF EGGS
JUST LIKE CHICKENS?
WE DON'T GROW
IN THE GROUND.
EVEN DEVIMON?
MM-HMM, UNFORTUNATELY.
WHAT'S THIS?
IT LOOKS LIKE
INSTRUCTIONS.
HUH?
IT'S WRITTEN
IN DIGICODE.
IT SAYS
"RUB GENTLY."
RUB GENTLY?
RUB WHAT, I WONDER.
YOU THINK MAYBE
WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO RUB THE EGG?
[SOFT VOCAL SOUNDS]
[MORE VOCAL UTTERINGS]
WOW!
WHY NOT
GIVE IT A TRY?
MAYBE A DIGITAL GENIE
WILL COME OUT.
I'M GONNA WISH
FOR A NEW SKATEBOARD.
HEY!
MMM...POHHHH!
IT JUST HATCHED!
NOW WE NEED
TO FIND HIM
HIS OWN CRADLE.
I'LL SEE IF THERE'S
AN EXTRA ONE.
OHH!
OH, SO THAT'S
HOW IT WORKS.
YOU'RE SAYING YOU DIDN'T
KNOW WHERE YOU CAME FROM
UNTIL NOW?
T.K., CAN YOU REMEMBER
THINGS FROM WHEN
YOU WERE A BABY?
UM...
HMM.
WELL, THESE PRETTY
SHAPES AND COLORS
DO REMIND ME OF SOMETHING
FROM A LONG TIME AGO.
IT WAS REAL SUNNY.
I WAS PLAYING WITH BLOCKS,
BUT I FELL OVER
OR SOMETHING,
AND I REMEMBER
I WAS CRYING.
[BABY CRYING]
BUT THERE WAS SOMEONE
THERE WITH ME...
SOMEONE. I DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHO.
MAYBE MY BROTHER MATT.
ANYWAY, SOMEBODY
PICKED ME UP,
AND I STOPPED CRYING.
ATTABOY.
THAT'S ABOUT ALL.
GUESS I DON'T
REMEMBER, EITHER.
YOU SEE?
OK, IT'S NOT SO EASY
REMEMBERING STUFF
FROM BEING A BABY.
AT LEAST I KNOW I DIDN'T
COME FROM AN EGG.
LET'S GO HATCH
SOME MORE DIGI-EGGS.
NOT THAT THERE'S ANYTHING WRONG
WITH HATCHING FROM AN EGG.
EUHHH!
SUPER THUNDERSTRIKE!
I AM ELECMON, CARETAKER
OF BABY DIGIMONS.
DON'T CROSS WIRES WITH ME.
THAT'S FISHING--NO WORMS,
NO HOOKS, NO WAITING.
[CHUCKLES]
COME ON, LITTLE FISHIES.
EVERYBODY OUT OF THE WATER.
LET'S GO.
HA HA HA HA!
THIS OUGHT TO BE ENOUGH
TO FEED THOSE LITTLE MOUTHS
FOR QUITE A WHILE.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
THAT'S IT. HA HA HA HA!
UHH! UHH!
UHH, UHH, UHH, UHH, UHH!
T.K.: HEY, WHAT'S WRONG?
OHH...OHHH...
ARE YOU HUNGRY?
ANHH! ANHH! ANHH!
T.K.: THAT
MUST BE IT.
UHHH...UHHH...UHHH...
[WHINING]
OH...
DON'T CRY.
YOU HAD
AN ACCIDENT.
HEY, PATAMON,
I COULD USE
SOME HELP OVER HERE.
SORRY, T.K.
NOT NOW.
[BABIES CRYING]
DON'T CRY.
OH, I'M SORRY.
FEEL BETTER.
I'M BUSY HERE.
BUT I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT BABIES.
YU! YU! YU! YU!
HEY! COME BACK!
[ELECMON GROANING]
CATCHIN' LOTS
OF FISH IS GREAT,
BUT HAULIN' 'EM ALL HOME
IS NOT.
HUH? MY BABIES
ARE ALL CRYING.
HANG ON, BABIES.
I'M COMING.
[BABIES CRYING]
IT'S OK.
BABIES, DON'T WORRY.
THERE.
INTRUDERS!
INVADERS!
WELL! I'LL TEACH THEM.
GET AWAY FROM THEM!
OH!
LOOK, PATAMON!
OH, MY!
RRRRHHH!
SUPER THUNDERSTRIKE!
BOY, HE'S ANGRY.
NO KIDDING.
SUPER THUNDERSTRIKE!
AAAH!
OHH!
[CHUCKLING MENACINGLY]
HEY, WATCH WHERE YOU'RE
AIMIN' THAT THING!
YOU COULD HURT SOMEBODY.
OF COURSE I COULD HAVE.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS
TRYING TO DO.
BUT WHY WOULD YOU
WANT TO DO ANYTHING
TO HURT US?
BECAUSE I SAW YOU
PLAYING WITH MY BABIES,
YOU INTERLOPERS.
SURE, WE PLAYED
WITH THEM.
BUT WHAT'S THAT GOT
TO DO WITH YOU?
YEAH.
UH, UH, UH, UH.
YOU BARBARIANS.
ALWAYS MAKING
THE SAME MISTAKE.
I'M NOT SOME
ORDINARY DIGIMON
WHO JUST HAPPENED
TO COME ALONG AND CATCH YOU.
THIS IS THE PRIMARY VILLAGE
HATCHLING GROUND AND NURSERY,
A VERY SPECIAL PLACE,
WHERE ALL DIGIMONS
START THEIR LIVES.
AND I'M A VERY
SPECIAL DIGIMON,
ENTRUSTED WITH CARING
FOR EACH AND EVERY ONE
OF THEM.
WELL, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
PLAY MR. BIG SHOT
AND FRY US.
I WAS ONLY
TRYING TO PROTECT
MY BABIES.
NOW, I THINK
THIS CONVERSATION
HAS LASTED
LONG ENOUGH.
I AM IN CHARGE,
AND YOU TWO
ARE TRESPASSING.
YOU MUST LEAVE.
NOW, NOW. DON'T
GET ALL PUFFY.
WHA? UHHH...
DON'T CALL ME PUFFY!
RRR! UHH!
AAH!
AAAHHH!
PATAMON, NO!
[THUD]
OHHH!
UNH! UNH! UNH!
THIS IS VERY BAD!
HE'S DIGIVOLVING!
AAH!
UNH! THAT HURT!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE DON'T WANT TO FIGHT.
WHAT'D WE DO?
MAN, THEY'RE FIGHTING
WORSE THAN MATT AND ME.
AND THEY'RE
NOT EVEN BROTHERS.
[FIGHTING
AND YELLING]
UHHHH...STOP IT!
[FIGHTING
AND YELLING]
HUH?
HMM?
FIGHTING'S NO GOOD
FOR SOLVING PROBLEMS,
YOU GUYS.
ALL YOU DID WAS
MESS UP YOUR FUR
AND SCARE
ALL THE BABIES.
[BABIES CRYING]
HMMPH! MY FUR
LOOKS FINE!
I'M SO SORRY,
LITTLE ONE.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO SCARE YOU.
HEY, PUNK,
YOU BETTER LEAVE
THOSE BABIES ALONE.
DON'T EVEN TALK
TO 'EM. GOT IT?
YOU KNOW WHAT I HEARD, PO PO?
TRYING TOO HARD TO ACT
GROWN UP IS A SIGN
OF IMMATURITY.
WHAT WAS THAT? HEY,
YOU GOT SOMETHIN'
TO SAY TO ME,
THEN SAY IT
TO MY FACE. DON'T
TALK BEHIND MY BACK.
COME ON,
OUT WITH IT,
YOU LITTLE
WING-HEADED 2-TONE
PORK CHOP.
TELL ME. OR DON'T
YOU HAVE THE GUTS?
RAHRR! NOT AGAIN.
T.K., CAN I?
CAN I PLEASE TEACH
THIS ARROGANT DIGITOAD
A LESSON?
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S GOING
TO LEARN SOMETHING.
DO YOU GUYS REALLY
HAVE TO DO THIS?
YES!
THEN WE HAVE TO DO IT
THE RIGHT WAY.
ALL RIGHT. I'VE GOT
A GREAT WAY TO SOLVE THIS.
MMMHHH!
RRRHH!
AND...NOW...
IN THAT CORNER,
THE DEFENDING CHAMPION--
ELECMON!
AND...NOW...
OVER IN THE OTHER CORNER...
THE CHALLENGER AND
MOST EXCELLENT DIGIMON...
PATAMON!
MHHHRRRHH!
ALL RIGHT! LET
THE TUG OF WAR BEGIN!
MMMMHHHH!
ON YOUR MARK!
GET SET!
AND GO!
KEEP PULLING.
PULL HARDER!
[THINKING] WHAT AM I
DOING THIS FOR?
[THINKING] I WON'T
LET HIM BEAT ME.
COME ON! COME ON!
[GRUNTING
AND GROANING]
MMM! MMM, MMM,
MMM, MMM!
[BOTH STRAINING
AND GROANING]
OHH!
OHHHHHHHHH!
OHHH!
T.K.: UM...ELECMON?
ARE YOU OK?
ELECMON?
UHHH!
Elecmon:
OK! I GIVE UP!
AND THE WINNER IS...
PATAMON!
YAY!
I'M CHAMPION!
[CHEERING]
Elecmon: YEAH,
YOU DID IT, KID.
YOU'RE THE TERROR
OF THE TUG OF WAR.
Patamon:
WANT TO TRY IT
ONE MORE TIME?
NOPE. YOU BEAT ME
FAIR AND SQUARE.
IT'S MY PLEASURE
TO WELCOME YOU
TO PRIMARY VILLAGE.
[CHUCKLES]
[CHEERING]
I'M REALLY SORRY,
PATAMON.
THERE'S NO GOOD EXCUSE
FOR THE MEAN WAY I ACTED
WHEN I FIRST SAW YOU,
BUT I'VE BEEN SO UPSET
ABOUT THINGS AROUND HERE.
EVER SINCE THE ISLAND
BROKE APART, I'VE BEEN
EXPECTING A FIGHT,
AND I GUESS I JUST
TOOK IT OUT ON YOU.
I APOLOGIZE.
AT LEAST KIDS MAKE UP
PRETTY FAST.
MY PARENTS ARE
STILL MAD AT ME...
FOR THE TIME I PAINTED
OUR KITTY CAT.
[CHUCKLES] YOU KNOW...
YOU'RE A LOT STRONGER
THAN YOU LOOK, KID.
I'M IMPRESSED.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY
YOU CAN'T TELL A COVER
BY THE SIZE OF ITS BOOK,
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
SURE. WELL, FORGET
ABOUT THE SAYINGS.
YOU'RE GREAT AT TUG OF WAR.
HEY...TAKE
A LOOK AROUND.
SOMEDAY ALL THIS
WILL BE YOURS,
PATAMON, MY BOY.
YOU'LL RAISE UP
SOME FINE YOUNG DIGIMON HERE,
JUST LIKE YOUR OLD MAN--
OH, ELECMON,
I AM NOT HERE
TO RAISE BABIES.
YOU'RE NOT?
I MEAN,
OF COURSE YOU'RE NOT.
[LAUGHING]
I WAS JUST...
OH, I GUESS
I WAS JUST DAYDREAMING.
BUT I WAS SERIOUS
ABOUT YOU STAYING HERE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE
TO GET SOME REST,
TAKE CARE OF THE BABIES...
WELL, YOU WON'T REST MUCH
IF YOU DO THAT.
YEAH. SOUNDS GREAT, ELECMON.
BY THE WAY, HOW DO WE
GET TO THAT MOUNTAIN?
IN...FINITY MOUNTAIN?
YES.
GULP! YOU ACTUALLY
WANT TO CLIMB UP THERE?
YES.
THAT'S REALLY
NOT A GOOD IDEA.
YOU NEED SPECIAL TOOLS,
CUSTOM HIKING BOOTS,
GLOVES, ALL VERY EXPENSIVE.
PLUS, YOU GOT
YOUR SNOW UP THERE.
THAT'S COLD.
AND POISON IVY
AND SNAKES AND BUGS
AND--OH, BIG BUGS AND--
T.K.: AND THERE'S DEVIMON.
YEAH, I WAS
GETTING TO THAT.
DEVIMON IS...
WELL, HE'S
AN EVIL DIGIMON.
T.K.: I KNOW, BUT I HAVE TO
ASK HIM ABOUT MY BROTHER
AND EVERYONE ELSE.
BUT HE WON'T
JUST TELL YOU. YOU'LL
HAVE TO FIGHT HIM.
I DON'T WANT
TO FIGHT EVER!
SURE. RIGHT.
THERE HAS TO BE
SOME OTHER WAY
TO FIND OUT.
WE NEED TO DO IT
WITHOUT FIGHTING
DEVIMON.
LIKE ASKING HIM
"PRETTY PLEASE"?
NO. IT'S NOTHING
LIKE THAT.
DO YOU REMEMBER
HOW IT FELT WHEN
WE WERE ALL LAUGHING?
YOU CAN'T HELP IT,
AND THE NEXT THING
YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT EACH OTHER
AND LAUGHIN',
AND YOUR CHEEKS ARE LIKE
YOU'VE BEEN BLOWIN' UP
BALLOONS ALL DAY.
LAUGHING'S THE BEST
PART OF FRIENDSHIP.
THAT'S IT!
HEY! WAIT!
T.K. IS RIGHT.
IT'S ALL ABOUT LAUGHIN'
AND BEIN' FRIENDS.
MAYBE WE CAN USE
THE POWER OF FRIENDSHIP
TO RETURN THE ISLAND
TO NORMAL.
I'VE GOTTA GO OVER
TO GIA SAVANNA WHERE
THE YOKOMON VILLAGE IS
AND TELL EVERYONE
RIGHT AWAY.
BYE-BYE,
AND BE CAREFUL.
IT'S JUST A FEELIN'...
BUT I REALLY
BELIEVE IN IT.
THANKS, T.K...AND
THANK YOU, PATAMON.
BYE-BYE!
[THINKING] MAYBE
HE CAN HELP US...
AND MAYBE I'LL GET
BACK TOGETHER WITH...
MY BROTHER.
I JUST KNOW MATT'S
OUT THERE SOMEWHERE.
I CAN ALMOST SEE HIM.
BUT I'VE GOT THIS YUCKY FEELING
THAT A LOT'S GONNA HAPPEN
BETWEEN NOW AND THEN.
Devimon: ALL BUT ONE
OF THEIR DIGIMON
HAVE DIGIVOLVED.
I MUST DESTROY THIS LAST ONE
BEFORE IT IS TOO LATE.
ARRRHHH! I CANNOT BELIEVE
IT HAS COME TO THIS.
STILL, AS LONG AS EVEN ONE
OF THOSE CURSED CHILDREN
IS LOST,
I AM PLEASED.
LEOMON!
MASTER?
I LEAVE THIS
TO YOU.
AS YOU WISH,
MY LORD.
WHAT SHALL I DO,
MASTER? WHAT TASK
DO YOU HAVE FOR ME?
NOTHING FOR THE MOMENT,
MY LOYAL SERVANT.
BUT SOON A BATTLE WILL RAGE,
AND YOU MUST BE PREPARED.
Ogremon: I UNDERSTAND,
MY LORD.
THIS TIME,
I WILL NOT FAIL YOU.
[CHUCKLING WICKEDLY]
NO. THIS TIME THERE
WILL BE NO FAILURE.
THIS TIME,
I SHALL BE VICTORIOUS!
HA HA HA HA HA!
MUH MUH MUH
BEH BEH BOH BOH.
BOH BOH BAH BAH.
WHAT IS IT?
BOH BOH
BUM BUM.
OHH!
[EXPLOSION]
HA HA!
HELLO! I'M COROVON!
T.K.: CONGRATULATIONS
ON DIGIVOLVING.
Babies: CONGRATULATIONS,
COROVON!
REMEMBER,
I'M YOUR DIGIMON, T.K.,
AND SOMEDAY
I'LL DIGIVOLVE, TOO
OH?
WOW. IS THAT BAD?
NO, BUT...
YOU WANNA DIGIVOLVE?
IS THAT WHAT
YOU'RE SAYIN'?
I'M JUST SAYING
IT MIGHT HAPPEN,
BUT
I DON'T REALLY
WANT IT TO.
I WANT TO STAY
LIKE THIS
FOREVER,
ALWAYS
BY YOUR SIDE.
MM-HMM! THAT'S SO AWESOME.
WE CAN BE BEST FRIENDS
FOREVER AND EVER.
OF COURSE.
WOW!
[BABIES CHEER
AND LAUGH]