Sora: AS WE FLOATED THERE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE OCEAN,
WE THOUGHT WE WERE DONE FOR.
THAT'S WHEN WHAMON RUSHED IN
TO WHISK US ALL OFF
TO THE SAFETY
OF THE BRINY DEEP,
BUT OUR BATTLE
WITH THE DARK MASTERS
WAS FAR FROM OVER.
THEY SENT THE DIVERMON
AFTER US,
AND SOON THEY WERE HOT
ON OUR TAIL.
WE LED THEM
ON A DEEP SEA CHASE,
BUT THE PRESSURE
WAS TOO MUCH FOR THEM.
WHEN WE FINALLY CAME UP
FOR AIR,
WE THOUGHT WE HAD MADE IT
TO SAFETY,
BUT AS BAD LUCK WOULD HAVE IT,
METALSEADRAMON HAD FOLLOWED US,
AND HE HAD OTHER IDEAS.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
SURRENDER!
I'M TIRED OF PLAYING AROUND
WITH YOU, WAR GREYMON.
SAY GOODBYE!
AAH!
[ ALL GASP ]
RIVER OF POWER!
[ GROANING ]
WHAMON!
NOVA FORCE!
RIVER OF POWER!
AAH!
SO MUCH FOR YOUR IMPENETRABLE
CHROME DIGIZOID ARMOR.
LOOKS TO ME
LIKE IT GOT A LITTLE RUSTY.
NEXT TIME YOU DECIDE
YOU WANT TO RULE THE WATERS,
DO EVERYBODY A FAVOR AND TAKE
A BUBBLE BATH INSTEAD.
WE WON.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
Whamon: DIGIDESTINED,
PLEASE SAVE THIS WORLD.
All: DON'T GO!
WHAMON --
WHERE DID HE GO?
LOOK THERE, EVERYONE.
Matt: IT'S HAPPENING
TO METAL SEADRAMON, TOO.
Sora: THEY'RE FLOATING
IN THE SKY.
Gomamon: I KNOW
WHERE THEY'RE GOING.
SPIRAL MOUNTAIN'S PEAK.
[ ALL GASP ]
NO. THAT'S THE REAL REASON
FOR ALL THE SHAKING.
OVER THERE.
All: HUH?
THE OCEAN.
IT'S, UH...
DISAPPEARING.
WELL, YOU DON'T
SEE THAT EVERYDAY.
TAG, I'M IT.
METAL SEADRAMON OUT,
PUPPETMON IN.
HA HA HA HA HA.
T.K.: LOOK, SPIRAL MOUNTAIN'S
OCEAN IS ALMOST COMPLETELY GONE!
Kari: BUT WHY?
THE DIGITAL OCEAN
IS BEING RECONFIGURED
BECAUSE WE KICKED
ITS DARK MASTER'S BUTT.
DOES THIS AFFECT US?
ABSOLUTELY.
IT CHANGES EVERYTHING.
IF WE'RE GOING TO GET ANY
SURFING IN, WE BETTER HURRY.
THOSE WIMPY DARK MASTERS
ARE NO THREAT TO SUPER JOE.
THAT'S THE DIGITUDE I LIKE
TO HEAR FROM YOU HUMANS.
LET'S GO.
All: YEAH!
Mimi: WAIT.
All: HUH?
WE'RE NOT
THROUGH HERE YET.
MIMI,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IN CASE YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
SOME OF OUR FRIENDS ARE GONE.
OH. SORRY.
THAT ONE
IS TO REMEMBER WIZARDMON.
THE ONE NEXT TO IT
IS FOR PIXIMON.
THAT ONE'S CHUUMON,
AND THIS ONE HERE
IS FOR WHAMON.
MIMI, THEY'RE NOT DEAD.
IT'S MORE LIKE
THEY'VE BEEN DOWNLOADED
TO A DIFFERENT COMPUTER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE DIGITAL.
OUR INFORMATION
JUST GETS RECONFIGURED.
WHAT BETTER REASON DO WE NEED
TO GET THE DARK MASTERS?
PAYBACK FOR MAKING
OUR FRIENDS LEAVE.
Mimi: I'M NOT GOING.
HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I HAVE HAD ENOUGH.
EVERY TIME WE FIGHT
WE WIND UP LOSING
ANOTHER FRIEND.
THIS IS WAR, MIMI,
AND SOMETIMES PEOPLE WE LIKE
GET HURT. SO DEAL WITH IT.
STOP IT, TAI!
WHY DON'T YOU STOP
AND THINK ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE'S
FEELINGS FOR A CHANGE?
HUH? WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WE KNOW YOU'RE RIGHT, TAI,
BUT GIVE US A LITTLE SPACE.
HUH?
WE MISS OUR FRIENDS
WHO FOUGHT ALONGSIDE OF US.
NOT EVERYONE HAS ICE RUNNING
THROUGH THEIR VEINS LIKE YOU!
WHA--
CALM DOWN.
YOU NEVER TAKE TIME
TO LOOK BACK.
WE'VE LOST
SOME GOOD FRIENDS HERE,
AND IT'S NICE TO REMEMBER
THEM ONCE AND A WHILE.
IF WE STOP TO DO THAT,
WE'LL NEVER HAVE TIME
TO SAVE THE WORLD.
YOU STILL DON'T GET IT.
YOU'RE NOT LISTENING.
STOP IT. YOU'RE MAKING
EVERYONE UPSET.
YOU TWO ARE SUPPOSED
TO BE FRIENDS.
WE'RE SITTING DUCKS OUT HERE.
LET'S FIND SOMEPLACE
A LITTLE LESS OUT IN THE OPEN.
[ Thinking ] I'M NOT AS COLD
AS MATT THINKS, AM I?
[ Thinking ] MAYBE I WAS
A LITTLE TOO ROUGH ON TAI,
BUT HE'S GOT TO RESPECT
OUR FEELINGS.
[ Thinking ] I'VE NEVER SEEN
MATT SO UPSET BEFORE.
[ Thinking ]
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
WE SHOULD BE CONCENTRATING
ON FIGHTING OUR ENEMIES,
NOT EACH OTHER.
[ Thinking ] I JUST KNOW
THEY'RE ALL THINKING ABOUT ME.
[ Thinking ] EVERYONE'S
SO TIRED AND CRANKY.
YOU OKAY?
WHA--
HMM.
WHY'D YOU STOP, KARI?
DID YOU HEAR
A NOISE JUST NOW?
WHAT KIND OF NOISE?
YOU MEAN YOU DIDN'T HEAR
SOMEONE SPEAKING A SECOND AGO?
YOU MEAN A VOICE?
NO. I DIDN'T HEAR
ANYTHING AT ALL.
WEIRD.
COME ON. LET'S GET BACK
TO THE OTHERS.
THERE'S SAFETY IN NUMBERS.
WHERE WERE YOU TWO?
I THOUGHT
I HEARD SOMETHING,
BUT IT WAS JUST
MY IMAGINATION.
IT'S DANGEROUS OUT HERE,
SO STAY WITH THE GROUP.
OKAY. I'M SORRY.
Puppetmon: IF THESE KIDS
TAKE ANY LONGER TO GET HERE,
I WILL DEVELOP WOOD ROT.
HAVE PATIENCE.
ROME WASN'T BUILT IN A DAY.
YEAH, BUT I WAS.
I'M TIRED OF WAITING.
HUH? WHAT'S THIS?
WHY ARE THE TREES
RUNNING SO FAST?
[ ALL SHOUT NERVOUSLY ]
WHAT IS GOING ON?
AAH!
THINGS AREN'T MOVING FASTER.
WE ARE.
THE GROUND WE'RE STANDING ON
IS ACCELERATING!
THIS IS MORE FUN
THAN THE TIME
I WAS FUMIGATED
FOR TERMITES. WHOO-HOO!
WHERE DID I PUT THOSE DOLLS?
I HAVEN'T SEEN THESE TOYS
SINCE I WAS A SAPLING.
WE GOT TO JUMP OFF!
Izzy: THIS PART'S MOVING!
SOMEONE'S TRYING
TO GET US SOMEWHERE,
AND IN A BIG HURRY.
WHY DO I GET THE FEELING
THAT SOMEONE'S
NOT TOO FRIENDLY?
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME I'VE
BEEN CARSICK WITHOUT A CAR.
I'VE GOT A PLAN.
THIS WAS ALWAYS GOOD
FOR A FEW LAUGHS.
MASTER!
YES, THAT'S VERY ENTERTAINING,
LORD PUPPETMON,
BUT THERE'S
NO SIGN OF THE CHILDREN.
WHAT?
THEY WERE HERE A SECOND AGO.
WHERE ARE THEY?
NOT HERE.
NOT HERE. I NEED
A NEW CABLE COMPANY.
[ GRUNTING ]
I HAVE A HUNCH
THAT ONE OF THE DARK MASTERS
IS BEHIND ALL THIS.
I'LL BET YOU'RE RIGHT.
Joe: I SAY WE EITHER KEEP GOING
OR BUILD A NEST.
WE HAVE TO FIGHT WHOEVER
IT IS SOONER OR LATER,
SO LET'S GET TO IT.
AGAIN WITH THE FIGHTING?
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO
TO A NEUTRAL CORNER?
PLEASE STOP ARGUING.
KEEP OUT OF THIS.
LET'S TRY IT YOUR WAY.
WE'LL STAY AND WAIT
FOR THE ENEMY TO GET US.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT!
STOP IT!
WHERE'D TAI GO?
HE DISAPPEARED.
OH, DID HE FALL?
HE VANISHED.
LOOK, NOW MIMI'S GONE.
MIMI, COME BACK!
MAYBE THEIR SCREEN SAVERS
ARE ON SLEEP.
JOE!
KARI!
EVERYBODY'S DISAPPEARED
BUT US.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OHH!
[ BOTH GASP ]
HUH? HOW'D WE GET
OVER HERE?
WE'VE BEEN TRANSPORTED.
AAH! I HATE MUD.
GATOMON!
I THINK IT'S OVER.
BUT NOW WE'RE SEPARATED
FROM EVERYONE ELSE.
DON'T WORRY. WE'LL BE
ALL RIGHT WITHOUT THE OTHERS,
ESPECIALLY TAI.
JUST STICK CLOSE TO ME,
AND I'LL PROTECT YOU,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
LISTEN, MATT, THE ONLY REASON
WE GOT THIS FAR
IS BECAUSE
WE WORKED AS A TEAM.
EACH OF US HAS PLAYED A PART
IN KEEPING US TOGETHER,
INCLUDING TAI.
BUT I, UH, UH --
AND I DON'T NEED YOU
TO PROTECT ME
ALL THE TIME EITHER.
I'VE GROWN UP A LOT.
I'VE FOUGHT ALONGSIDE
YOU GUYS,
AND I'VE HELD MY OWN.
T.K., THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEANT.
WHAT I -- WHAT I WANTED
TO SAY WAS --
WHAT?
[ Thinking ]
I'M PUSHING EVERYONE AWAY.
Puppetmon: ONE, TWO, THREE,
YOU'RE STILL IN THE TREE.
YOU KNOW, KIWIMON,
THIS ISN'T AS MUCH FUN
AS I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
I SHOULD JUST
DESTROY THEM ALL.
THEN YOU WON'T HAVE
ANYONE LEFT TO PLAY WITH.
GOOD POINT.
AAH!
OHH!
JOE!
[ LAUGHING ]
HEY, JOE,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
IT'S MY STOMACH.
WHAT'S WRONG?
DOES IT HURT?
NO, I'M JUST DOING THIS
'CAUSE IT'S FUN!
Puppetmon: I'VE GOT A NEW GAME
I WANT TO PLAY. COME HERE.
YOU, TOO.
WHOA!
OH, BROTHER.
AND FOR YOU!
AAH! STOP MOVING!
THIS IS LIKE PLAYING CHESS
WITH THE DIGIDESTINED.
KARI!
HELP! OHH!
FASCINATING.
MAYBE FOR YOU.
WHERE AM I?
WE'VE REACHED
THE TURNING POINT.
IMPOSSIBLE.
WELCOME BACK.
Puppetmon:
COOCHIE-COOCHIE-COO!
[ LAUGHING ]
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S SO FUNNY,
BUT THIS IS
NO LAUGHING MA-- UHH!
MATT, YOU'RE BACK.
T.K.!
I'M GETTING TIRED
OF DOING NOTHING.
I WON'T BE SOME CAT
STUCK IN A TREE.
LET'S GO LOOK FOR THEM.
I'LL START
BY LOOKING FOR T.K.
THIS IS AWFUL.
YOU SAID IT.
HOW COULD IT GET ANY WORSE?
I'LL TELL YOU HOW.
THE BRANCHES ARE
STARTING TO CRACK.
THEY SHOULD LEARN
TO FLY.
I THINK I FOUND
A NEW TOY TO PLAY WITH.
HE LOOKS VERY EASY
TO SCARE.
YOU WANT ME
TO GET HIM FOR YOU?
NO, I'LL GET
THIS ONE MYSELF.
[ LAUGHING ]
T.K., ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I GUESS SO. I FELT LIKE
SOMETHING WAS TICKLING ME.
I COULDN'T STOP LAUGHING.
I WONDER IF THERE'S
SOMETHING WRONG WITH ME.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE NOT HURT?
STOP BEING
SO WORRIED ABOUT ME.
I TOLD YOU BEFORE I KNOW HOW
TO TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
OKAY.
Puppetmon: HEY, T.K.!
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
T.K., STAY CLOSE.
TIME TO PLAY!
SOUNDS LIKE THE VOICE
IS GETTING CLOSER.
AAH!
TIME TO PLAY!
IT'S YOU!
KEEP YOUR HANDS
OFF MY BROTHER, PUPPETMON,
OR I'LL CHOP YOU
INTO FIREWOOD.
OH, COME ON. BE NICE.
ALL I WANTED TO DO
WAS PLAY A LITTLE
GAME OF WAR WITH T.K.
OH, PLAY?
YOU MEAN, LIKE PRETEND?
BUT OF COURSE! AT LEAST,
IN THE BEGINNING,
IT WILL BE
MAKE-BELIEVE, ANYWAY.
THEN IT'S BYE-BYE,
AND IT WILL BE TIME
TO DESTROY YOU FOR REAL.
IF I GOT RID OF YOU NOW,
I'D HAVE NO FUN.
HE'S TRYING TO SCARE YOU.
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM.
DON'T LIE TO HIM,
OR YOUR NOSE WILL GROW.
I CAN'T MOVE NOW!
ARE YOU OKAY?
MATT!
NOW SHALL WE GET GOING?
FORGET IT!
YOU DON'T WANT TO? HMM.
WELL, IF YOU DON'T COME
WITH ME, IT'S NO FUN.
MAYBE INSTEAD I'LL
DESTROY YOUR BROTHER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
OKAY, I'LL COME.
THAT'S A GOOD BOY.
T.K., IT'S A TRAP. RUN AWAY
NOW WHILE YOU STILL CAN!
SHUT UP. IS IT A DEAL?
WE'LL HAVE LOTS OF FUN.
[ MUFFLED GRUNTING ]
Puppetmon: NOW YOU HIDE,
AND I'LL SEEK AND DESTROY.
[ GASPING ]
THAT'S GOOD. KEEP RUNNING.
YOU MAKE THE GAME INTERESTING.
HEY, SOMEONE'S COMING.
WHO COULD IT BE?
SOUNDS LIKE LORD PUPPETMON
HAS FOUND A NEW PLAYTOY.
OH, HI THERE. BYE.
BY THE WAY,
I'M HIDING BACK HERE,
SO DON'T SAY ANYTHING,
OKAY?
NO PROBLEM.
HEY, YOU GUYS,
YOU DIDN'T HAPPEN TO SEE
A LITTLE KID RUN BACK HERE,
DID YOU?
Blossomon: NO, WE DIDN'T SEE
ANYTHING LIKE THAT, BOSS.
WE SAW A KID WEARING
A BACKPACK AND A GREEN HAT.
LOSERS! COME OUT, COME OUT,
WHEREVER YOU ARE!
AHA!
HEY, LOOK, A HOUSE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE FOREST.
I WONDER IF ANYONE INSIDE
HAS SEEN T.K.
WHOA!
AAH!
WHAT'S GOING ON
AROUND HERE?
All: JOE! MIMI!
MATT!
T.K.! T.K. WAS TAKEN
PRISONER BY PUPPETMON!
OH, NO!
WE HAVE TO HELP HIM.
WHERE'D THAT CREEPY
LITTLE TOOTHPICK TAKE T.K.?
I DON'T KNOW!
GET A HOLD
OF YOURSELF, MATT.
IT SHOULDN'T BE
THAT DIFFICULT TO FIND HIM.
I'M SURE THAT FIRST ROAD
WE WERE ON LEADS TO PUPPETMON.
THEN WE'LL ALL
BE TRAPPED.
IT'S WORTH IT
TO SAVE T.K.
I AGREE.
LET'S GO GET HIM.
WHO ARE YOU?
NO ONE MAY INTERFERE
WITH MASTER PUPPETMON'S
PLAY TIME. YOU'RE STAYING HERE.
Tentomon:
OH, NO, IT'S KIWIMON,
AN ANCIENT DIGIMON
THAT WAS SAID TO BE EXTINCT.
ALTHOUGH HE'S
A BIRD-TYPE DIGIMON,
HIS WINGS HAVE DEGENERATED,
SO HE CAN'T FLY.
PUMMEL PACK!
[ CHIRPING ]
AAH!
KOROMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
AGUMON!
HAVE SOME PEPPER BREATH!
SPIRAL TWISTER!
ELECTRO SHOCKER!
AAH!
BLUE BLASTER!
HMM.
I WONDER WHAT
THESE DOLLS ARE FOR.
THIS ONE LOOKS LIKE JOE.
JOE, WHAT HAPPENED?
WHY DOES THIS STUFF
ALWAYS HAPPEN TO ME?
WEIRD. I DIDN'T
SEE ANYONE PUSH YOU.
JOE'S ON TV? LET'S SEE
WHAT ELSE IS ON.
OH. HMM.
NOW, THAT'S WHAT I CALL
REMOTE CONTROL.
[ GASPING ]
YOO-HOO!
AAH!
THERE YOU ARE.
I FOUND YOU.
THE GAME'S OVER.
OHH.
I'M GOING TO DESTROY YOU
IN A MINUTE,
BUT FIRST, I HAVE
TO SCRATCH MY LEG.
THAT'S WHAT I GET
FOR HAVING A LEG
MADE OF POISON OAK.
[ Thinking ]
I CAN OUTSMART HIM.
HOW BORING. I'M NOT HAVING
ANY FUN AT ALL.
WHAT? I'M THE LIFE
OF THE PARTY.
I PUT THE "FUN"
IN "FUNGUS."
HA! YOU JUST PLAY
THE SAME GAME
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
BORING!
I'M NOT BORING.
HOW COME YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY REAL FRIENDS?
I'VE GOT FRIENDS.
THEN HOW COME
I HAVEN'T MET
THESE SO-CALLED FRIENDS
OF YOURS?
ALL RIGHT, I'LL GET THEM
AND INTRODUCE YOU RIGHT NOW.
T.K.!
PATAMON!
I LIKE TO MAKE FRIENDS.
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU
KEEPING T.K.?
[ LAUGHING ]
ANSWER ME!
I KNOW HOW
YOU FEEL, MATT,
BUT FIRST WE HAVE
TO DEFEAT KIWIMON.
HOW CAN YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW I FEEL?
I UNDERSTAND THAT IF WE
DON'T BEAT HIM FIRST,
WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO FIND T.K.
NO! FIRST, WE FIND T.K.,
THEN WE'LL FIGHT YOUR WAR!
RIGHT, MATT.
GABUMON WARP DIGEVOLVE TO --
HUH?
THEY WON'T GLOW.
WHAT'S GOING ON
HERE, MATT?
HOW COME
I CAN'T DIGEVOLVE?
PUMMEL PACK!
[ CHIRPING ]
THERE. DONE. I SAID
I LIKE TO MAKE FRIENDS,
AND I'VE MADE ONE.
I BROUGHT MY FRIEND!
LOOK!
HUH?
T.K.?
IT'S LORD PUPPETMON'S
NEW TOY.
WHERE'S HE GOING?
WE'RE GOING TO PLAY CHARADES.
MAYBE HE DOESN'T KNOW
HOW TO PLAY.
[ CHIRPING ]
AAH!
BIYOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
BIRDRAMON!
[ CHIRPING ]
METEOR WING!
BIRDRAMON, THANKS A LOT!
YOU'RE WELCOME.
BIYOMON.
Matt: BIYOMON,
WHAT DID YOU DO?
LOOK WHAT
YOUR DIGIMON DID.
WITHOUT KIWIMON,
WE'LL NEVER FIND T.K.
CALM DOWN, MATT.
T.K.: HEY!
IT'S T.K.
HEY, EVERYBODY!
HI! I'M BACK!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
SEE, EVERYBODY?
I TOLD YOU I COULD DO IT.
I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF
JUST FINE.
YOU'RE THE MAN!
NICE GOING, T.K.
GREAT JOB, BUDDY.
WE WERE WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
FOR A LITTLE KID,
THAT WAS A PRETTY BIG ESCAPE.
STOP IT, GUYS.
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME.
WHAT'S WRONG, MATT?
I ALSO SMASHED
THE REMOTE CONTROL
THAT WAS MAKING THE GROUND
MOVE UNDERNEATH US.
THAT'S TERRIFIC, T.K.
T.K.: EVERYTHING'S GOING
TO BE ALL RIGHT NOW.
PUPPETMON WAS USING
THESE DOLLS TO CONTROL US.
THAT'S WHY THOSE
WEIRD THINGS WERE HAPPENING.
IS THIS ME? I DON'T LOOK
ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
WOW, MIMI, YOUR DOLL
IS REALLY PRETTY.
WHAT? NO WAY. I WOULD
NEVER WEAR RAGS LIKE THIS.
OH! I COULD TAKE HER
TO THE MALL
FOR SOME NEW CLOTHES.
[ LAUGHING ]
Both: ALL RIGHT, YOU GO.
SO HE DIDN'T WANT TO PLAY
WITH ME, HUH?
T.K., YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS.
ANYBODY SEE
WHERE MATT WENT?
HE'S RIGHT OVER THERE.
All: HUH?
Joe: I DON'T GET IT.
HE AND GABUMON WERE THERE
A SECOND AGO.
THEY VANISHED.
HERE WE GO AGAIN.
WILL PUPPETMON
TAKE REVENGE ON T.K.?
IS HE
BEHIND MATT'S DISAPPEARANCE?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS."