SO EVERYONE
WAS FINALLY REUNITED,
EXCEPT SORA.
SHE WAS STILL UPSET
BECAUSE DEMIDEVIMON TOLD HER
THAT HER CREST OF LOVE
WOULD NEVER GLOW.
DEMIDEVIMON AND MYOTISMON
UNLEASHED A VICIOUS ATTACK
AND REALLY HURT BIYOMON.
THE REST OF THE DIGIMON
TRIED TO HELP,
BUT MYOTISMON
WAS TOO POWERFUL.
BIYOMON WANTED TO FIGHT,
BUT SORA PROTECTED HER.
THAT'S WHEN SHE REALIZED
SHE WAS ACTING LIKE A MOM,
PROTECTING SOMEONE SHE LOVED.
HER CREST THEN BEGAN TO GLOW,
HELPING BIRDRAMON DIGEVOLVE
TO GARUDAMON
AND STOPPING
MYOTISMON'S ATTACK.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERs ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
[ HUMMING ]
Joe: HEY, CHECK IT OUT, MIMI.
HOW ABOUT THIS
FOR AN INSTANT BATH?
GEE, NOW YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO GO SOAK YOUR HEAD
THE NEXT TIME YOU HAVE
AN ALLERGY ATTACK.
RIGHT. THAT WAS SO FUNNY,
I FORGOT TO LAUGH.
NOW THAT MYOTISMON'S
CHASING US,
WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO KEEP RUNNING
LIKE CRAZED SHOPPERS
AT THE MALL.
HE'S A BIG CREEP,
IF YOU ASK ME.
I AGREE WITH YOU.
YEAH, HE'S
SMALL POTATOES FOR US.
MY WISH IS TO NEVER
SEE HIM AGAIN PERIOD.
MINE, TOO.
Izzy: GATHER AROUND,
EVERYONE.
Tai: I HOPE LUNCH IS READY
BECAUSE I'M STARVING.
GENNAI'S BACK.
HE WANTS TO SPEAK TO US.
IS THIS A SCHEDULED VISIT?
DON'T KEEP US IN SUSPENSE.
WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
I've brought you some good news
and some bad news.
Which would you like
to hear first?
Joe: SAVE THE GOOD NEWS
FOR LAST.
Matt: HE'S A BASKET CASE
ANYWAY.
LET'S START
WITX THE GOOD NEWS.
You all look like
you could use some cheering up.
I've been told another child
will be joining your group.
WHO TELLS YOU
THESE THINGS ANYWAY?
Well, this is someone
you shall want as a friend.
This someone
is a DigiDestined.
REALLY?
I HOPE THIS NEW ONE
WILL HAVE A DIGIMON
THAT WILL BE ABLE
TO HELP US.
YOU AND ME BOTH.
The important thing
to remember
is all eight of you
must be together.
As long as you are separated,
the worlds will not be
in harmony with each other.
Everything will go wacko,
so we must find
that other child.
HOW DO WE DO THAT?
I HOPE
IT'S SOMEONE MY SIZE.
I HOPE SHE'S MY SIZE
SO WE CAN SWAP CLOTHES.
TELL US SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS KID,
LIKE WHAT'S HIS
OR HER NAME?
Uh, the name?
YEAH.
It's...I forgot.
[ ALL YELLING ]
GENNAI!
Calm down.
I do know the location
of the child.
It's Japan.
HUH?
JAPAN?
WHERE IS JAPAN?
JAPAN'S A BIG ISLAND
IN THE FAR EAST.
AGUMON AND TAI
WERE TRANSPORTED THERE
WHEN OUR TWO WORLDS
CONVERGED.
IF THEY EVER
CONVERGE AGAIN,
MAYBE WE'LL ALL
GET TO GO HOME.
Remember,
that was the good news.
CAN'T WAIT
TO HEAR THE BAD.
of the eighth child
Myotismon has heard
and will be going
to Japan soon.
He's gathering his forces
as we speak.
If he gets
to the child first,
both of our worlds
will be doomed.
DOOMED? WE NEED SOME SPIES
ON THE INSIDE.
[ CHATTERING ]
THE NOODLE-BRAINER TEAM!
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL WHIP THEM ALL INTO SHAPE.
THESE DWEEBS
WILL BE UNBEATABLE
WHEN I GET THROUGH WITH THEM.
NANIMON
IS AN INVADER DIGIMON.
I'D TELL HIM
WHAT I REALLY THINK
ABOUT HIS SUNGLASSES,
BUT HIS POWER PUNCH
WOULD FLATTEN ME.
WE KNOW
YOU CAN TALK THE TALK,
BUT NOW IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO DO YOUR STUFF.
JUST WATCH.
I DON'T WANT TO.
CAN I HELP YOU TWO?
Together: YEP.
WE'RE RENEGADE SOLDIERS
LOOKING FOR A BATTLE.
WE MAY LOOK SILLY,
BUT UNDERNEATH
OUR COOL EXTERIOR,
WE'RE FIGHTING MACHINES.
IS THAT SO? WHO ARE YOU?
I'M PUNKAGUMON.
I'M REGGAEGUMON.
Together: YEAH!
WHAT A COUPLE
OF WEIRDOS.
YOU'RE PERFECT.
I'LL TAKE YOU.
YEAH! COOL! HA HA HA!
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
COME IN.
MYOTISMON, I HAVE SOME
GOOD NEWS TO REPORT.
THE SOLDIERS ARE ASSEMBLED,
AND WE'RE READY
TO MOVE OUT.
ARE THEY WORTHY OF ME?
YES, MY MASTER.
HA HA HA!
THEY'RE A BUNCH
OF HELPLESS SEA SLUGS,
IF YOU WANT MY OPINION.
WHO ARE YOU?
GREETINGS, LITTLE BLUE ONE.
HUH?
GATOMON!
GATOMON MIGHT LOOK LIKE
A HARMLESS LITTLE KITTY,
BUT DEEP DOWN INSIDE
SHE'S AN OUT-OF-CONTROL
WILDCAT.
DON'T EVER CROSS HER PATH.
JUST WHERE DID YOU MANAGE
TO FIND THAT GROUP
OF GOOFBALLS ANYWAY?
YOU COULD DO BETTER?
WITH MY PAWS TIED.
GATOMON, DON'T WASTE
YOUR TIME ON HIM.
HAVE YOU DONE
WHAT I'VE ASKED OF YOU?
YES. PER YOUR INSTRUCTIONS,
I SEARCHED EVERYWHERE
AND FOUND THE MOST FEROCIOUS
DIGIMON I COULD FIND.
YOU'LL BE VERY PLEASED.
I KNEW I COULD TRUST YOU.
I LOOK FORWARD
TO MEETING THEM.
THANKS.
[ GROWLING ]
WHAT IS IT?
WE'VE PREPARED THE ROOM.
IT'S READY FOR INSPECTION.
FINE. THE TWO OF YOU
ARE DISMISSED.
RIGHT.
[ GROWLING SOFTLY ]
All: AH! OH!
HA HA HA!
IF YOU DON'T MIND MY ASKING,
WHAT IS THIS ROOM FOR?
LEGENDS TELL
OF THIS HALLOWED GATE.
IT IS THE PASSAGEWAY
THAT WILL TAKE US FORWARD
TO THE OTHER WORLD.
WHEN WE PASS THROUGH
THIS PORTAL,
WE'LL BE FREE TO INFILTRATE
THE HUMAN REALM.
According to my information,
the gate to the other world
should be somewhere
inside this castle.
MY THEORY IS THAT MYOTISMON
SENT DEMIDEVIMON
TO DISTRACT US
WHILE HE STAYED BEHIND
TO PREPARE THE GATE.
TRULY AN INGENIOUS PLAN
ON HIS PART.
AGUMON AND PALMON
HAVE CERTAINLY BEEN GONE
A LONG TIME.
IT'S NOT THAT I'M WORRIED,
IT'S JUST THAT, WELL,
I HOPE THEY'RE LOOKING
FOR THE LOCATION
OF THE GATE.
I'M WILTING.
I WANT TO GET OUT
OF HERE NOW.
NOW HOP LIKE BUNNYMON!
COME ON! COME ON! HOP IT!
GET THE JELLY
OUT OF YOUR LEGS!
THIS BATTLE'S GOING
TO BE BIG,
SO GET WITH IT.
YOU GOTTA TRY
LIKE NEVER BEFORE.
HE'S RIGHT.
WE NEVER TRIED BEFORE.
SO WHY SHOULD WE
START NOW?
EVERYBODY THAT MOUTHED OFF
WILL GO WITHOUT DINNER TONIGHT.
YOU DO UNDERSTAND ME,
DON'T YOU?
NO WAY!
THE FOOD'S THE ONLY REASON
WE JOINED THIS DORKY ARMY
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
MM-MMmMM.
I'D LIKE TO SOAK IN A HOT TUB
FOR ABOUT TWO MONTHS.
I'VE GOT BLISTERS
ON MY BLISTERS.
I THINK WE HAVE
TO STOP THIS GUY...
♪ AND I KNOW HOW
TO DO IT ♪
YEAH?
I WAS A SOLDIER
WITH HIM BEFORE.
HE LIKES TO DRINK SODA,
BUT THE BUBBLES GO RIGHT
TO HIS HEAD
AND MAKE HIM AS DIPSY
AS A DOODLEMON.
HE'LL DO ANYTHING YOU WANT.
I MUST BE EXHAUSTED.
I THOUGHT I SAW
A LITTLE PINK THING
POP UP AND TA
HIS STOMACH WILL FILL
WITH BUBBLES.
YEAH, HE'S SURE TO EXPLODE.
WON'T HE MAKE US HANG AROUND
AND CLEAN IT UP?
FORGET THE MESS.
WE CAN ALL ESCAPE.
ONE OF US SHOULD GO
GET SOME SODA.
HE WON'T MISS
ONE OF US.
AFTER THAT SLOB
WOULDN'T LET US HAVE DINNER,
I'LL POUR THEM
DOWN HIS THROAT MYSELF.
NEXT UP -- CONTACT SPORTS.
HOW ABOUT WRESTLING?
YOU'RE THE BOSS!
I WONDER WHERE --
THERE IT IS.
HA HA HA!
THIS IS WHAT HE GETS
FOR NOT FEEDING US.
YOU GUYS ARE PATHETIC.
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE TIRED.
[ ALL GROANING ]
YOU'RE A WORTHLESS PACK
OF GOONS.
WHAT IN THE WORLD?
OH, BOY!
ME LIKES ORANGE.
DELICIOUS!
HA HA HA.
HAVE SOME MORE.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ BELCHES ]
AHH.
HA HA HA HA!
HEY, ANYBODY WANT
TO GO DANCING?
I'M LIGHT ON MY FEET.
All: GO! GO! GO! GO!
HOO! HO!
HOO-HOO! HEH!
HA! LOVE tHAT SODA!
HO-WHOA!
IT WO2KED!
All: YEAH!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE...
BEFORE HE WAKES UP.
YEAH.
BUBBLE FIZZ
WON'T LAST FOREVER.
I'M WORRIED.
JUST BE PATIENT.
HEY, LOOK, THEY'RE BACK!
SORRY, WE HAD A BIG BRUISER
ON OUR HANDS.
LET'S GO!
My signal is useless
inside the castle,
so you are on your own.
WE GOT IT COVERED.
You must stop Myotismon
from carrying out his plans
and protect your friend
in Japan.
Palmon: WE BETTER MOVE IT.
I MUST FIND THE SECRET
TO THE GATE.
ONCE I UNDERSTAND
THE MEANING OF THESE CARDS,
THE KEY WILL OPEN THE LOCK.
THEN I WILL BE ABLE
TO ENTER THE PATH
TO THE HUMAN WORLD.
YOU DIGIDESTINED
THINK YOU'RE SO SMART,
BUT IN REALITY, I AM ALWAYS
ONE STEP AHEAD OF YOU.
HA HA HA.
I'VE GOT A REAL FUNNY FEELING
ABOUT THIS, YOU GUYS.
THINK SOMETHING'S WRONG?
SOMETHING JUST
DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
[ ALL GASP ]
MAKING ANY PROGRESS, JOE?
NO. THIS LOCK'S ANCIENT,
BUT I STILL
CAN'T BREAK IT.
MAYBE IF WE HAD THE KEY
IT WOULD OPEN.
YEAH, AND MAYBE
IF WE HAD A CANNON,
WE COULD BLAST
OUR WAY IN.
IT'S NO USE.
MAYBE THERE'S
ANOTHER WAY IN.
LET'S CHECK.
JOE, LET'S GO.
HOW COME I NEVER
GET TO BE THE HERO?
SOMETHING'S
TOTALLY WEIRD HERE.
WHAT?
WE'VE PASSED
THIS WAY BEFORE.
Izzy: IS THAT YOU, TAI?
HAVE YOU FOUND ANYTHING
UNUSUAL DOWN THERE, IZZY?
WELL, YOU COULD SAY THAT.
THE TRUTH IS
YOU'RE WAY DOWN THERE
AND WE'RE UP HERE.
I THINK YOU GUYS
MAY NEED GLASSES.
WE'RE WAY UP HERE
ABOVE YOU.
BUT THERE'S NO WAY.
THAT'S SCIENTIFICALLY
IMPOSSIBLE.
[ SCREAMING ]
I'M READY TO PROCEED.
TELL OUR FORCES
NO SACRIFICE IS TOO GREAT
IN THIS MOMENT OF GLORY.
RIGHT.
THERE'S CERTAINLY NO NEED
TO TELL THEM
THAT THEY WON'T BE SHARING
IN THE REWARDS.
I HOLD ALL THE CARDS,
AND THEY ARE
NO LONGER A MYSTERY.
NOW ALL I NEED
IS TO FIND
THAT DIGIDESTINED
EIGHTH CHILD.
MY THEORY IS MYOTISMON
SET UP THESE OPTICAL ILLUSIONS
TO DETER US
FROM FINDING THE GATE.
I'D SAY HE SUCCEEDED.
WE'RE STILL AS LOST
AS WE WERE
BEFORE WE STARTED.
ALL WE'VE DONE SO FAR
IS GO IN CIRCLES,
AND WE DON'T KNOW UP
FROM DOWN.
HUH?
WHAT'S UP?
SOMEONE'S COMING.
YOU SURE?
YOU DOUBT ME?
[ ALL GASP ]
I'M ITCHING TO FIGHT.
THEY SEEM TO KNOW
WHERE THEY'RE GOING.
MAYBE WE SHOULD TRY
TO FOLLOW THEM.
THEY'LL LEAD US
TO THE RIGHT PLACE.
I SHALL NOW BE EMBARKING
ON A JOURNEY TO ANOTHER WORLD.
THERE ARE FORCES
WHICH MUST BE NEUTRALIZED
BEFORE OUR VICTORY HERE
CAN BE COMPLETE.
BUT NEVER FEAR --
I SHALL RETURN IN TRIUMPH.
[ CHEERING ]
IT'S TIME TO STAND BACK
AND WATCH ME WORK MY MAGIC.
OPEN THE GATE
TO MY DESTINY!
COMPANY, MOVE!
HMM.
Tai: YOU'RE NOT
GOING ANYWHERE,
NOT AS LONG
AS WE CAN HELP IT.
WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
DO YOU WORK FOR ME?
CAN'T YOU SEE I'M BUSY
AT THE MOMENT?
YEAH, RIGHT!
DEMIDEVIMON, WOULD YOU
PLEASE TAKE CARE
OF THIS ANNOYING
GANG OF HOODLUMS?
OF COURSE, SIR.
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
I'M AT YOUR SERVICE.
I'M NOT LETTING YOU
GET PAST THIS GATE.
FAT CHANCE,
YOU LITTLE TWERP.
I'VE BROUGHT REINFORCEMENTS.
IT'S ALL YOURS, NANIMON.
RIGHT. DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT PASSING BY ME.
YOU GOT IT?
FAREWELL, DIGI-DOOMED.
OKAY, LET'S FIGHT!
WE DON'T WANT
TO FIGHT YOU GUYS,
BUT THE FUTURE
IS AT STAKE.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
AGUMON DIGEVOLVE TO GREYMON!
PALMON DIGEVOLVE TO TOGEMON!
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
GOMAMON DIGEVOLVE TO GARURUMON!
TENTOMON DIGEVOLVE
TO KABUTERIMON!
GOMAMON DIGEVOLVE
TO IKKAKUMON!
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS --
DIGIMON ♪
I ORDER EVERYONE
BACK INTO RANKS!
I'LL BUY YOU DINNER.
COME ON.
TOO LATE NOW.
WE'RE GOING
FOR SOME FAST FOOD.
WHOA! YOU'RE BIG!
ANYBODY NEED
A WRESTLING COACH?
HY, yOU CAN'T RESIGN.
YOU WANT TO BET?
WHEN
TO HAVING MY FANNY KICKED,
I'M OUT OF HERE.
IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME,
YOU MIGHT CHECK THE FINE PRINT
ON MY CONTRACT.
WE'RE COMING THROUGH!
DON'T LET ME STAND
IN YOUR WAY!
YOU MIGHT AS WELL GIVE UP.
I'M OUTNUMBERED!
GOOD HELP
IS SO HARD TO FIND.
JUST ADMIT YOU PICKED
THE WRONG SIDE
AND GIVE IT A REST.
IF YOU'RE TRYING
TO FRIGHTEN ME,
IT WON'T WORK.
YOU HAVEN'T DEALT
WITH ME YET.
THAT WAS TOO EASY.
TRY THIS!
[ GIGGLING ]
TO THE GATE, EVERYONE!
WE'VE GOT TO GET THROUGH!
HEY, I DON'T THINK SO.
[ ROARING ]
DEVIDRAMON --
HE'S ONE NASTY DRAGON
AND GUARDIAN OF THE GATE.
DEVI DOESN'T LIKE LOSING,
AND IF YOU WANT A REAL SURPRISE,
LOOK INTO HIS EYES.
YOU'LL BE HYPNOTIZED.
[ ALL GASP ]
NOVA BLAST!
HOWLING BLASTER!
ELECTRO SHOCKER!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
HAD ENOUGH?
NEEDLE SPRAY!
HUH? I'M STARTING
TO FEEL REALLY WEIRD?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
[ ALL MOANING ]
[ GROWLING ]
HOW ABOUT THAT
FOR SOME AWESOME FIGHTING?
WE GOT YOU BEAT BY A MILE.
THE GATE'S CLOSING!
NOVA BLAST!
HOWLING BLASTER!
[ SCREECHES ]
MOVE IT,
YOU FLYING BEAN BAG!
I'M GOING THROUGH!
BOOM BUBBLE!
THIS WAY!
HUH?
COME TO PAPA,
LIZARD BREATH!
WE HAVE TO MAKE
A RUN FOR IT.
READY, GET SET, GO!
HUH?
GO THROUGH IT.
OH...
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
GREYMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
METALGREYMON!
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
METALGREYMON!
[ ROARS ]
YOU'RE THE MAN!
♪ DIGIMON -- MONSTER FRIENDS
TO THE BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
HURRY!
♪ CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
GIGABLASTER!
[ SCREECHING ]
♪ CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
HE DID IT.
IT'S CLEAR SAILING
FROM HERE.
COME ON, EVERYBODY.
LET'S GET THROUGH THAT GATE.
ALL RIGHT!
GET YOUR MITTS OFF OF ME!
AAH!
STAND BACK!
GET OUT OF OUR WAY!
SORRY, BUT YOU'RE TOO LATE.
I'LL MISS YOU IN JAPAN.
[ ALL PANTING ]
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
GET READY TO JUMP.
HURRY.
THE GATES ARE CLOSING.
GOODBYE.
UHH!
[ GROWLING ]
OH, NO.
THIS CAN'T
BE HAPPENING.
NO! OPEN UP! OPEN!
IT CAN'T BE!
[ CRYING ]