DIGIMON.
GATOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
DIGEVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE.
ANGEWOMAN!
MAGNA ANGEMON!
MEGAKABUTERIMON!
LILLYMON!
ZUDOMON!
GARUDAMON!
GABUMON
WARP DIGEVOLVE TO...
AGUMON
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
WARP DIGEVOLVE.
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
METALGARURUMON!
WARGREYMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
WE'RE BACK!
WHAT?
YOU'RE DEALING WITH
THE NEW AND IMPROVED
DIGI-DESTINED!
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
HOW DID YOU DIGEVOLVE
WITHOUT YOUR CRESTS?
NOTHING'S IMPOSSIBLE --
NOT WHEN YOU'VE GOT
YOUR FRIENDS HELPING YOU.
YOU SAID IT, MATT.
NOW -- TIME TO FIGHT!
All: YEAH!
THEY'RE DOOMED!
SO YOU WANT TO FIGHT?
DEATH CLAW!
VULCAN'S HAMMER! AAH!
ALL RIGHT!
YOUR HAMMER NAILED IT!
WE CAN HELP OUT, TOO,
RIGHT, LILLYMON?
HANG ON!
HANG ON FOR WH-- AAH!
FLOWER CANNON!
NEXT TIME CAN YOU USE
SOMEONE ELSE AS A BOOMERANG?
SORRY, BUT I WANTED
TO MAKE SURE YOU CAME BACK.
VULCAN'S HAMMER!
TAI, NOW'S YOUR CHANCE
TO GO FOR HIS BODY!
ALL RIGHT!
HUH?
JOE, MIMI, LOOK OUT
BEHIND YOU!
HUH?
GATE OF DESTINY.
CELESTIAL ARROW!
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, GUYS.
WE'RE HERE TO PROTECT YOU.
WE'LL GO FOR THE OTHER
CLAWS, TOO.
WE OWE YOU ONE.
MATT, THIS IS BETTER
THAN ANY VIDEO GAME!
I'LL SAY.
DEATH CLAW!
Lillymon: FLOWER CANNON!
HEY, WHY SHOULD YOU GUYS
HAVE ALL THE FUN?
SAVE SOME
FOR ME AND IZZY!
WE'LL DISTRACT APOCALYMON
WHILE MATT AND TAI
CONCENTRATE ON ATTACKING.
WATCH OUR BACKS!
LET'S END THIS.
VIRUS GRENADES!
MEGAKABUTERIMON
PROTECT SORA!
GOT IT.
WING BLADE!
GRR!
THANKS, GUYS.
GIGA CANNON!
NOW IT'S MY TURN.
HORNBUSTER!
GRR!
ATTACK!
NOW!
METAL WOLF CLAW!
TERRA FORCE!
AAH!
WE DID IT! WE DESTROYED
ALL OF HIS CLAWS!
STILL THINK
YOU'RE SO TOUGH?
HA HA HA HA.
IS THAT YOUR BEST SHOT?
YOU KNOW YOU'RE BEATEN.
FACE IT LIKE A MON.
YOU THINK SO, HUH?
WELL, I MAY BE BEATEN,
BUT I WON'T GO DOWN THAT EASILY.
I'LL TAKE YOU
AND BOTH WORLDS WITH ME!
WHAT?
YOU STILL HAVEN'T SEEN
MY ULTIMATE ATTACK --
TOTAL ANNIHILATION!
[ Thinking ] HE'S GOING
TO DESTROY EVERYTHING.
I SHOULD HAVE
MADE OUT MY WILL.
I'M TOO GOOD-LOOKING
TO GO!
I WANT MY MOMMY.
THERE MUST
BE A SOLUTION.
WE WON'T GIVE UP.
WE'RE STRONGER
THAN HE IS.
WE'RE A TEAM.
IT'S DESTINY.
AFTER ALL...
All: WE'RE THE DIGI-DESTINED!
WHAT WAS THAT?
I'M NOT SURE.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE EXPLOSION?
IT WAS COMPLETELY CONTAINED
BY THE POWER
OF OUR DIGIVICES.
THEN IT'S OVER.
WE ACTUALLY WON.
LOOKS THAT WAY.
EXCUSE ME
WHILE I THROW UP.
WE SAVED THE WORLD.
MM-HMM.
HEY! YOU DID IT!
REMIND ME TO CALL YOU
THE NEXT TIME
I HAVE TROUBLE
WITH MY LANDLORD.
IT WAS NOTHING.
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
WELL, I DID HAVE
SOME HELP, YOU KNOW.
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
[ SOBBING ]
GREAT, BRO.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
SORRY I'M LATE.
FORGOT TO SET MY ALARM.
IS IT OVER?
All: YEAH!
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD NOW?
SEE FOR YOURSELVES.
LOOK DOWN.
All: HUH?
IT'S FILE ISLAND!
THE ANCIENT PROPHECY SAID
THAT AFTER
THE GREAT DARKNESS IS OVER,
THE FIRST THING TO BE REBORN
WILL BE THE ISLAND,
AND FROM THAT ISLAND WILL
COME THE LAND AND THE SEAS.
YEAH, BUT WHAT
DOES THAT MEAN?
IT MEANS THAT THE DIGIWORLD
WILL START OVER
FROM THE BEGINNING.
WHAT'S HAPPENING
DOWN THERE?
THE DIGIWORLD
IS BEING REBORN,
AS ARE ALL THE DIGIMON
FROM THE PAST.
WE'RE GOING TO NEED
A LOT OF DIAPERS.
ALL RIGHT! LET'S GO!
All: RIGHT!
IT'S THE PRIMARY VILLAGE.
AND EVERYTHING'S
BACK TO NORMAL.
IT'S STARTING TO RAIN.
AH! A DIGIEGG STORM!
HA HA HA!
WAIT! THOSE EGGS
ARE MY RESPONSIBILITY!
ARE YOU GOING
TO COUNT THEM ALL?
YOU NEVER COUNT YOUR
DIGIEGGS BEFORE THEY HATCH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HELPING
THESE DIGIEGGS HATCH.
ARE YOU GOING
TO HATCH THEM ALL?
OF COURSE WE'RE GOING
TO HATCH THEM ALL.
THE FUTURE OF THE DIGIWORLD
DEPENDS ON IT.
YAY! YOU CAN HELP.
JUST RUB THEM GENTLY.
THIS IS FUN.
WE SHOULD BE DONE
IN 60 YEARS.
THIS MEANS LEOMON
WILL BE REBORN.
THAT'S RIGHT!
AND PIXIEMON, WEYMON,
AND WIZARDMON, TOO!
YES, SOMEDAY.
WE SHOULD TAKE A PICTURE
TO COMMEMORATE
THIS SPECIAL OCCASION.
A PICTURE? GOOD IDEA.
SURE, LET'S DO IT.
I'M IN.
GREAT. I'LL GO GET
T.K. AND KARI, THEN.
I'LL SHINE MY HEAD.
HA HA HA HA.
ALL RIGHT. WE'RE READY.
SAY "CHEESE."
[ GASPS ]
WHAT'S WRONG?
[ ALL GASP ]
WHAT IS IT?
LOOK. IT HATCHED.
IT'S SO CUTE.
BO. BO.
[ ALL LAUGH ]
I'M OUT OF HERE.
All: HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU'RE LEAVING?
IT'S TIME TO HIT THE ROAD,
MAKE LIKE A TREE AND LEAVE.
BUT, OGREMON, WHY NOT
STAY HERE WITH US?
LOOK, I'M A VIRUS-TYPE
DIGIMON.
YOU GUYS ARE DATA
AND VACCINE TYPES.
IF I HANG AROUND
TOO LONG,
I'LL GET SICK
TO MY STOMACH.
CATCH YOU LATER.
HE JUST CAN'T FACE
THE FACT THAT HE LIKES US.
I'VE NEVER HEARD
OF A VIRUS
GIVING SOMEONE
A COLD SHOULDER.
DON'T SAY THAT.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE DAY
DAGUMON FIRST DIGEVOLVED?
AT THE TIME, I SAID IT WAS
THE WRONG THING TO DO,
BUT THE TRUTH IS
WHEN IT COMES TO DIGEVOLVING,
THERE IS NO RIGHT OR WRONG.
A DIGIMON'S DESTINY
CANNOT BE CHANGED.
THAT DAY WAS
A REAL EYE-OPENER FOR ME.
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO OPEN THEM SINCE.
WELL, IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN NEXT TIME,
I'LL JUST DIGEVOLVE MYSELF
INTO THE NEXT DARK MASTER.
NO, NO!
[ ALL LAUGH ]
BO. BO.
THIS SURE BRINGS BACK
A LOT OF MEMORIES.
THIS IS THE EXACT SPOT
WHERE WE SPENT
OUR FIRST NIGHT
HERE IN THE DIGIWORLD.
THIS IS WHERE GABUMON FIRST
DIGEVOLVED INTO GARURUMON
AND FOUGHT SEADRAMON.
YEAH, AND THIS IS THE PLACE
WHERE I FAINTED
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
THE FIRST TIME
IN THE DIGIWORLD.
IT SURE IS GREAT STROLLING
DOWN MEMORY LANE, ISN'T IT?
HEY, DO YOU THINK,
WHEN WE ALL GET BACK,
WE'LL BE SOME KIND
OF HEROES
AND WIN A BUNCH OF AWARDS
LIKE AN EMMY OR SOMETHING?
JOE!
SORRY. OH, DOPEY ME.
OPEN MOUTH, INSERT FOOT.
I MEAN, WE CAN ALWAYS
COME BACK, RIGHT, GUYS?
RIGHT?
JOE.
OH, I FORGOT.
FAUX PAS.
TIME PASSES DIFFERENTLY HERE
THAN IN OUR WORLD.
YOU GUYS WILL PROBABLY
BE LONG GONE.
OOPS. THERE GOES
THE OTHER FOOT.
HEY.
WE'VE STILL GOT
A LOT OF SUMMER LEFT.
I WAS THINKING
MAYBE WE COULD STAY HERE
UNTIL
OUR VACATION'S OVER.
YEAH!
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
IF MATT'S STAYING,
I'M STAYING, TOO.
ME, TOO.
IS THAT OKAY, TAI?
SURE.
I'M STAYING, TOO.
ME, TOO.
WE MIGHT AS WELL.
WE'VE GOT PLENTY OF TIME.
SINCE AN ENTIRE DAY
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
IS EQUAL TO ONE MINUTE
IN THE REAL WORLD,
AND WE'VE GOT FOUR WEEKS
LEFT OF SUMMER VACATION...
THEN WE CAN STAY HERE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
FOR UP TO...
LET'S SEE, CARRY THE FOUR,
DIVIDE BY THREE...
A REALLY LONG TIME.
TO BE PRECISE,
IT'S 40,320 DAYS.
THAT'S ABOUT 110 YEARS.
ALL RIGHT!
WE'RE STAYING!
All: YAY!
HEY, LOOK.
IT'S AN ECLIPSE.
YES, IT IS,
AND THERE'S SOMETHING
VERY IMPORTANT YOU SHOULD KNOW
ABOUT IT, CHILDREN.
I KNOW! YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO LOOK DIRECTLY INTO IT.
TRUE.
THAT'S NOT ALL.
THIS ECLIPSE COULD
COST YOU YOUR LIVES.
IT'S NOT
AN ORDINARY ECLIPSE?
THAT SHADOW IS THE GATE
THAT CONNECTS YOUR WORLD
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
I'M AFRAID THE ECLIPSE
WILL ONLY LAST TWO MORE HOURS.
WE'LL JUST WAIT
UNTIL IT OPENS UP AGAIN.
YEAH.
WE STILL HAVE OVER 100 YEARS
OF SUMMER VACATION LEFT.
ACTUALLY,
WHEN APOCALYMON APPEARED,
THE FLOW OF TIME HERE
AND IN YOUR WORLD
BECAME SYNCHRONIZED.
SO THEN WE STILL HAVE
FOUR WEEKS LEFT, RIGHT?
THAT'S PLENTY OF TIME
TO HAVE FUN.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
YOU ONLY HAVE THE TWO HOURS.
ONCE THE PORTAL IS CLOSED,
IT'S CLOSED FOREVER.
BUT --
SORRY. IT'S TIME
TO SAY GOODBYE.
OHH!
I'M SURE
GOING TO MISS YOU, SORA.
SAY HI TO YOUR MOM
WHEN YOU GET BACK.
SURE. I WANT TO THANK YOU,
BIYOMON.
BEFORE I MET YOU,
I DIDN'T GET ALONG WITH MY MOM.
WE ARGUED. SHE WOULD
NEVER LET ME DO ANYTHING,
BUT THANKS TO YOU,
I UNDERSTAND HER
A LOT BETTER.
YOU SHOWED ME HOW MUCH
MY MOM REALLY LOVES ME.
YOU MEAN IT?
HA HA. OF COURSE.
THAT MAKES ME SO HAPPY
TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
SOMETIMES I THOUGHT
I WAS JUST BOTHERING YOU
AND GETTING IN YOUR WAY
ALL THE TIME.
DON'T BE SILLY.
YOU WEREN'T A BOTHER.
YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND.
BIYOMON, I'M GOING
TO MISS YOU SO MUCH.
I KNOW IT'S
GOING TO BE HARD
TO FIND A FRIEND
AS GREAT AS I AM, GOMAMON,
BUT YOU'LL HAVE TO TRY.
NOT A PROBLEM.
I TOOK AN AD OUT
IN THE PERSONALS.
I'VE GOT
FIVE INTERVIEWS.
MM.
WHAT?
AT LEAST
LET'S SHAKE HANDS.
OKAY, FOR LUCK.
[ Hums ]
WOW!
WHAT?
FOR SOMEONE
WITHOUT A HAND,
YOU'VE GOT
A PRETTY STRONG GRIP.
HA HA HA HA.
Both: HA HA HA HA.
TENTOMON?
YES, IZZY?
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL YOU
BEFORE WE PART WAYS.
OKAY, I LOVE YOU.
YAA!
TENTOMON, ARE YOU OKAY?
YES, I'M FINE, BUT I WAS
A LITTLE TAKEN ABACK
BY YOUR SUDDEN
DISPLAY OF EMOTION.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I DON'T USUALLY
GET EMOTIONAL,
BUT THIS WAS
A UNIQUE OCCASION.
I KNOW HOW MUCH OUR FRIENDSHIP
HAS MEANT TO US.
IN THE NAME
OF OUR FRIENDSHIP,
I NEED TO ASK YOU
ONE LAST FAVOR.
WOULD YOU PLEASE TURN OFF
THOSE WINDSHIELD WIPERS?
SURE THING, PAL.
ANYTHING FOR YOU.
GIVE ME A HUG.
AAH! AAH!
YOU'RE CHOKING ME!
[ SOBBING ]
T.K., PLEASE STOP CRYING.
YOU'RE MAKING ME CRY.
I WAS JUST CRYING
BECAUSE YOU WERE CRYING.
WELL, IF YOU'RE CRYING
BECAUSE I'M CRYING
AND I'M CRYING
BECAUSE YOU'RE CRYING,
THEN NEITHER ONE OF US
NEEDS TO BE CRYING.
OH. OH, YEAH.
BESIDES, I'M SURE WE'RE
GOING TO SEE EACH OTHER AGAIN.
LIKE WE SAW
EACH OTHER AGAIN
AFTER THAT THING
WITH DEVIMON.
THAT'S RIGHT, WE DID.
LET'S MAKE A PACT.
WE'LL SEE EACH OTHER AGAIN.
PROMISE?
PROMISE.
Both: HA HA HA HA.
HMM. HMM.
MMM.
HMM.
THAT SAYS IT ALL.
MM-HMM.
I WOULDN'T
MIND HEARING YOU
PLAY YOUR HARMONICA
ONE LAST TIME.
GLAD TO.
[ HARMONICA PLAYING ]
[ SOBBING ]
STUPID MATT
AND HIS HARMONICA.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
N-NOTHING.
YEAH, SURE.
HEY, COME OVER HERE
AND LOOK AT THIS.
THIS IS WHERE I FIRST MADE
MY PEPPER BREATH, REMEMBER?
REMEMBER?
HOW COULD I EVER FORGET?
THAT'S WHERE YOU
BURNED SEADRAMON'S TAIL,
AND HE ATTACKED US.
YOUR AIM HASN'T GOTTEN MUCH
BETTER SINCE THEN, EITHER.
HEY, YOU DON'T REALLY
BELIEVE THAT, DO YOU?
MM, WELL, LOOK
AT THE BRIGHT SIDE.
YOUR AIM HAS GOTTEN
ANY WORSE.
COME ON, TAI.
Both: HA HA HA HA HA.
FOR ME?
UH-HUH.
HERE, LET ME
PUT IT ON YOU.
IT DOUBLES
AS A FLEA COLLAR.
THANKS, KARI.
IT LOOKS GOOD ON YOU.
GEE, THANKS.
OH, WELL,
I GUESS THIS IS...GOODBYE.
YEAH,
TILL NEXT TIME.
NEXT TIME?
YEP, THAT'S RIGHT.
HUH?
PALMON,
WHERE ARE YOU?
I WANT SO SAY GOODBYE!
HUH? PRINCESS MIMI,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
PALMON'S DISAPPEARED.
HAVE YOU SEEN HER?
NOT RECENTLY.
SORRY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW SHE COULD LEAVE
AT A TIME LIKE THIS.
THERE'S ONLY
A FEW MINUTES LEFT.
PALMON,
WHERE ARE YOU?
I'M LEAVING SOON!
MIMI.
[ WHIMPERS ]
Gennai: HAVE YOU ALL FINISHED
SAYING YOUR GOODBYES?
YOU CAN TAKE
THIS CABLE CAR HOME
ON ONE CONDITION --
YOU HAVE TO PROMISE TO BRING IT
BACK TO SAN FRANCISCO
WHERE I BORROWED IT FROM.
[ SOBBING ]
WELL, UH...
CAN'T WE JUST HAVE
A LITTLE MORE TIME?
PLEASE, GENNAI,
DO SOMETHING.
I'M SORRY, SORA.
THE GATE
WON'T WAIT ANY LONGER.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
PALMON SEEMS
TO HAVE DISAPPEARED.
WHY WOULD SHE RUN AWAY?
WHY?
[ SOBS ]
[ SOBBING ]
PALMON, SO THAT'S
WHERE YOU'RE HIDING?
MIMI'S BEEN
LOOKING FOR YOU.
YES, I KNOW,
BUT I DON'T WANT
TO SEE HER.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IF I DON'T SEE HER,
THEN SHE CAN NEVER
SAY GOODBYE TO ME.
IS THAT WHAT
YOU REALLY WANT?
I'M AFRAID YOU'LL
REGRET IT ONE DAY.
IT'S TOO PAINFUL
TO SAY GOODBYE.
I'M SORRY, MIMI. WE CAN'T
WAIT FOR PALMON ANY LONGER.
IT'S TIME.
GET ON THE CABLE CAR,
EVERYONE.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
Mimi: [ SOBS ]
WELL, GUYS, THIS IS IT.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
TRY GOODBYE.
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
GOODBYE!
TAKE CARE!
DON'T LET ANYONE
PUSH YOU AROUND!
MAKE SURE
YOU DRESS WARM!
GOODBYE!
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING!
[ SOBBING ]
MIMI!
MIMI, LOOK!
MIMI! MIMI!
PALMON!
MIMI, I'M SORRY!
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT!
GOODBYE, PALMON!
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING!
I LOVE YOU!
GOODBYE, MIMI -- OHH!
[ GASPS ]
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ THE MONSTER FRIENDS
TO THE BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ THE CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ ULTIMATE FRIENDS
TO THE BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ THE CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ SEVEN YOUNG KIDS
GO TO CAMP FOR THE SUMMER ♪
♪ WIND UP LIVING
IN A DIGITAL LAND ♪
♪ WHERE EVERYBODY GETS TO MEET
HIS OWN DIGIMONSTER ♪
♪ A DIGITAL COMPANION,
A DIGITAL FRIEND ♪
♪ A DIGIMON IN TRAINING
WILL DIGEVOLVE TO ROOKIE ♪
♪ AND DIGEVOLVE TO CHAMPION
AND ULTIMATE, TOO ♪
♪ GONNA SAVE
THE DIGITAL WORLD FOR ME ♪
THE DIGITAL WORLD FOR YOU ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ MONSTER FRIENDS
TO THE BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ THE CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ ULTIMATE FRIENDS
TO THE BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ THE CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
OUR ADVENTURE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
MIGHT BE OVER FOR NOW,
BUT THAT GATE
WON'T STAY CLOSED FOREVER.
I HAVE A FEELING THAT
THIS WON'T BE THE LAST TIME
WE SEE OUR PALS THE DIGIMON.
YOU WAIT AND SEE.
ONE DAY THAT PORTAL
WILL OPEN UP AGAIN
AND WE'LL RETURN
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
I WONDER IF AGUMON
WILL REMEMBER ME?
I KNOW
I'LL NEVER FORGET HIM
OR THE REST OF THE DIGIMON.
NONE OF US WILL.