Sora:
WE WERE STILL IN THE DESERT
TRYING AVOID ETEMON AND HIS DARK NETWORK
WHEN A BIG SHIP PULLED UP.
WE GOT ON BOARD
AND EVERYTHING WAS FINE--
AT LEAST WE THOUGHT SO--
BUT THE SHIP WAS JUST A TRAP
SET UP BY KAKATREEMON.
HE USED HIS PETRIFIER
AND TURNED SOME OF US TO STONE!
FORTUNATELY,
NOTHING BEATS A GOOD DIGIVOLVE!
WE SENT KAKATREEMON FLYING
AND A WELL-PLACED CACTUS
TOOK CARE OF THE SHIP.
THE NEXT CREST TURNED OUT
TO BE FOR MIMI
THEN SHE REALIZED HOW IMPORTANT
SHE WAS TO OUR ADVENTURE.
♪ DI-DI-DI,
DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE INTO
DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE-- ♪
♪ ( bird cry ) ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Tai:
OKAY, I ADMIT A LITTLE BREEZE
WOULD BE NICE,
BUT IT'S STILL
A BEAUTIFUL DAY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
MAYBE FOR A SCORPION.
Mimi:
IT'S BEAUTIFUL,
ISN'T IT, JOE?
EVERY CREST WE'VE FOUND SO FAR
HAS BEEN DIFFERENT.
YEAH--BUT WE NEED
TO LEARN HOW TO USE THEM.
OR OUR DIGIMON COULD DIGIVOLVE
ALL MESSED UP, RIGHT?
Matt:
BUT NONE OF THAT REALLY MATTERS
UNTIL WE FIND ALL THE CRESTS.
HMM--I THINK YOU'RE
RIGHT ABOUT THAT ONE.
MAYBE THE CREST POWER
COMES FROM HAVING THEM ALL.
HMM...
WHAT ARE THEY
DOING BACK THERE?
HEY! WE GOTTA MOVE ON.
IF WE'RE GONNA
TAKE SOME DOWNTIME,
WE NEED TO FIND SOME SHADE!
WE'RE RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF
A SERIOUS DIGICONVERSATION
AND YOU MADE ME FORGET
WHAT I WAS SAYING.
YOU FIND THE SHADE--
WE'LL CATCH UP.
WHOA!
T.K.:
WHAT HAPPENED?
Joe:
SOMETHING GRABBED THEM
FROM UNDERNEATH!
( all gasp )
Matt:
IT'S KUWAGAMON!
RRRRR!AAAH!
AAAH!
RRRRR!
GRRRR!
IS THAT THE SAME ONE, REALLY?
Palmon:
IT'S KUWAGAMON, ALL RIGHT-
THERE'S NO MISTAKING
THAT UGLY FACE.
BUT HE'S SURE IS BIGGER
THAN HE WAS THE LAST TIME.
GRRRR!
PEPPER BREATH!
AARRGGH!
GRRR!
WE HAVE A BIG PROBLEM--
THIS GUY IS MUCH STRONGER
THAN HE USED TO BE.
NO! NOW! DIGIVOLVE!
AGUMON DIGIVOLVE TO GREYMON!
ALRIGHT--RETHINKING
OUR TRAINING PROGRAM HERE...
Tai:
OH MAN--I HOPE AGUMON
DOESN'T FREAK OUT.
WHAT IF
SOMETHING'S WRONG WITH ME,
WHAT IF I CAN'T
BECOME GREYMON?
AGUMON, STAY AWAY
FROM HIS CHOPPERS!
( roaring )
MOVE AGUMON! MOVE!
DO SOMETHING! GET BACK!!
GOTCHA!
NICE ONE.
GRRRR!!!
OOOOH!
Piximon:
PIXIE BOMB, SEEK AND DESTROY!
( Kids and digimon
sigh with relief )
All:
ARE YOU OKAY? MY GOODNESS!
WHAT JUST
HAPPENED TO US?
DUM-DUM-DUM, DUM-DEE-DUM,
DUM-DUM-DUM, DUM-DEE-DUM...
HUH?
Mimi:
A POWDERPUFF WITH WINGS!
JUST DON'T
USE IT ON YOUR FACE.
WHERE'S KUWAGAMON?
OH MAN--
MAYBE THAT'S HIM!
I AM NO ENEMY, NOPE, NOPE--
IF ANYTHING,
YOU ARE YOUR OWN ENEMIES.
I'VE HEARD OF YOU,
YOU'RE THE FAMOUS PIXIMON!
YOU ARE?
Biyomon:
PIXIMON IS FAMOUS
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
FOR HIS SKILLS AND TRAINING,
BUT FEW HAVE EVER MET HIM.
HIS SECRET HOME
IS THE TRAINING GROUND
FOR ALL
THE GREAT DIGIMON FIGHTERS!
I'VE HEARD ALL ABOUT YOU, TOO,
BUT SO FAR I AM NOT IMPRESSED!
HUH!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
THE DIGI-DESTINED--HAH!
YOU'D BETTER BE MORE CAREFUL
OR YOU'LL END UP DIGI-DINNERS!
YEP, YEP--
WITHOUT MY SPEARS AND MAGIC,
KUWAGAMON WOULD BE EATING YOU
WITH A SIDE OF DIGI-FRIES!
THAT'S GROSS--
THANKS A LOT.
AND THAT'S NOT ALL,
YOU DIGIMON THERE.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
PROTECTING THE CHILDREN,
BUT HALF THE TIME
THEY'RE PROTECTING YOU.
I WANT TO SEE SOME GUTS!
THIS GUY REMINDS ME OF
A GYM TEACHER I ONCE HAD.
HE'S RIGHT--
WE JUST DON'T HAVE ANY GUTS.
Gomamon:
DON'T WE GET
POINTS FOR ENTHUSIASM?
THE NEWS ISN'T ALL BAD--
YEP, YEP--
FROM NOW ON,
YOU'RE ALL GONNA TRAIN WITH ME!
BUT WHY?
LET'S NOT GO OVERBOARD.
ESPECIALLY YOU TWO GUYS.
HUH?!
WHAT?!
YOU TWO NEED LOTS OF HELP,
AND I HAVE A SPECIAL EXTREME
TRAINING PROGRAM JUST FOR YOU.
DID I HEAR HIM RIGHT?
SOUNDS EXTREME.
YEP--FOLLOW ME!
DUM-DUM-DUM, DUM-DEE-DUM...
All:
WHADDYA THINK? WHADDA WE DO?
Joe:
DO WE TRUST
A PING PONG BALL WITH WINGS?
Tai:
BUT HE DID
SAVE AGUMON AND ME--
HE WOULDN'T DO THAT
IF HE WAS NO GOOD.
Izzy:
HE DIDN'T HAVE A BLACK GEAR
ANYWHERE ON HIM--I CHECKED.
Joe:
WHAT DO YOU SAY, BIYOMON?
YOU SEEM TO KNOW ABOUT HIM.
Biyomon:
IT'S AN HONOR TO BE CHOSEN
BY PIXIMON FOR TRAINING.
Mimi:
SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF WORK.
Sora:
HE'S RIGHT THOUGH--
WE COULD USE SOME HELP.
Tai:
HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
JUST 'CAUSE' WE'VE
NEARLY BEEN EATEN 100 TIMES!
Matt:
THERE ARE WORSE OPTIONS--
DO WE HAVE A CHOICE?
ALL IN FAVOR SAY AYE.
All:
AYE!
JUST HURRY UP!
Mimi:
ARE WE THERE YET?
Piximon:
JUST A LITTLE FURTHER.
Joe:
THAT'S THE 7TH TIME
HE'S SAID THAT.
Matt:
I THINK HE'S LOST.
Tai:
SO WHAT DO WE DO? ASK A CACTUS
FOR DIRECTIONS?
Sora:
ICE CREAM, COLD ROOT BEER...
All:
STOP THAT!
HALT! WE HAVE ARRIVED!
YEP!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING HERE.
PIXIE PORTAL--HA HAA!!
HA HA HA HA HA!
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
( gasping )
Mimi:
IT'S A HOLE IN THE DESERT!
Joe:
AM I THE ONLY ONE WHO THINKS
THIS LOOKS LIKE TROUBLE?
Piximon:
IT'S JUST MY FRONT DOOR--
COME ON IN,
BEFORE IT CLOSES--YEP YEP!
MM-HMM.
Tai:
COOL--A JUNGLE INSIDE A DESERT.
ALL YOUR FRIENDS
MUST WANT TO PLAY HERE!
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN IT
WHEN I FIRST GOT IT.
HUH?!
HEADS UP--
BEHIND US, GUYS!
( all gasp )
Mimi:
OH NO--IT'S ETEMON
AND HIS TRAILER!
THIS IS BAD!
AND RIGHT OUTSIDE THE FRONT DOOR
HE IS, TOO.
HUH?
DON'T WORRY--HE ISN'T ABLE
TO SEE THROUGH THE BARRIER.
HE SEES NOTHING BUT THE DESERT.
THE STUPID SCREEN
IS STILL BROKEN--
WE'VE ALMOST GOT IT FIXED--
NO NEED FOR A CONNIPTION FIT.
I'LL SHOW YOU CONNIPTION,
YOU INSOLENT WORM!
FIX IT!
I'VE GOT A SHOW TO PUT ON!
Piximon:
ALRIGHT, HOME WE ARE--
MY HOME IS JUST UP THESE STEPS.
( all gasping )
Joe:
WE HAVE TO WALK UP THERE?!
Mimi:
BUT I DIDN'T BRING
MY STAIR-CLIMBING SNEAKERS!
Tai:
AND I JUST REMEMBERED--
I'M AFRAID OF HEIGHTS.
Izzy:
FROM A LOGICAL STANDPOINT,
IT'S DOESN'T LOOK VERY SAFE.
Sora:
IS THIS PART OF OUR TRAINING?
EXACTLY!
( all groaning )
HEY, NO SWEAT--
I'LL JUST FLY UP THERE.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT
I'LL BE CHILLIN' BY THE POOL--
BY THE WAY--
DID I MENTION
THERE'LL BE NO FLYING BY ANYONE
DURING TRAINING?
HAVEN'T YOU ROOKIES LEARNED
THAT THE EASY WAY
IS SOMETIMES A TRAP?
NOW LET'S MOVE OUT!
( all groaning )
Joe:
I GUESS PIXIMON
NEVER HEARD OF ELEVATORS.
( panting )
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE ALL TIRED!
DON'T GIVE UP YET!
YOU SEE?
YOU'VE ALMOST ARRIVED!
THAT'S HIS PLACE?
THAT'S IT, AND THERE'S
PLENTY OF FOOD FOR ALL.
All:
HEY, ALRIGHT! YEAH!!
Piximon:
WHY, THANK YOU--IS IT
AS HANDSOME AS ME? HA HA!
Joe:
YOU SAID SOMETHING ABOUT FOOD?
YES, BUT FIRST
YOU MUST EARN IT.
Gomamon:
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
THERE'D BE A CATCH.
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
HA HA HA HA HA HA HA!
I WANT YOU ALL
TO SCRUB THE FLOORS...
ALL
THE FLOORS!
All:
NO! OH, MAN!
IT'LL TAKE FOREVER!!
BUT NOT YOU, AGUMON AND TAI--
COME NOW--I HAVE A SPECIAL TOUR
FOR THE TWO OF YOU.
GREAT--WE PROBABLY HAVE TO
PAINT THE PLACE.
Mimi:
THE LAST TIME I SCRUBBED
A FLOOR WAS....NEVER.
Izzy:
IT'S A SIMPLE TASK, MIMI,
EVEN YOU'LL CATCH ON.
IS THIS TRAINING,
OR IS PIXIMON'S MAID OFF TODAY
AND HE DOESN'T LIKE TO VACUUM?
T.K.:
TOKOMON,
LET'S HAVE A CLEANING RACE--
READY, SET, GO!
VROOM!
VRRROOOOMMMM!!!!
( chuckling )
Piximon:
ALL RIGHT, YOU TWO,
THIS IS THE PLACE, YEP YEP!
COME ON INTO THE CAVE!
HMM...
IT'S PITCH-BLACK IN HERE!
WHAT KIND OF A CHORE
CAN WE DO IN HERE?
WE WON'T BE ABLE TO SEE
OUR HANDS IN FRONT OF OUR FACES!
WHOA!
Piximon:
THIS IS YOUR TRAINING.
YOU MUST FIND YOUR WAY BACK.
( snoring and sleeping sounds )
HUH?
SHHH!
Matt:
SOMETHING'S WRONG--
TAI AND AGUMON NEVER CAME BACK.
SO WHAT
DO YOU THINK HAPPENED?
WHOA!
YOU SEE THAT?
PRODIGIOUS!
WHEN THEY GLOW,
IT MEANS THE CRESTS ARE NEARBY.
ARE YOU SURE
THIS IS SMART, MATT?
I MEAN, MAYBE WE SHOULD BRING
TENTEMON AND GABU--
LET 'EM SLEEP--THE CRESTS
MUST BE INSIDE THE BARRIER,
SO WE'RE SAFE.
COME ON, IZZY,
THIS WAY!
HMM...
TAI! WAKE UP!
HEY--WHERE ARE WE?
WE WERE IN A CAVE,
BUT I DON'T REMEMBER A BOAT.
HEY!
HELLO!!!
WHOA!
HEY!
DON'T YOU KNOW
NOT TO STAND UP IN A BOAT?
HERE--GRAB THIS.
HUH?
DO YOU SEE THAT LIGHT?
DON'T LOOK AT THE LIGHT--
PULL ME IN!
HEY, DON'T ROCK THE BOAT--
OH!!
NOW LOOK WHAT YOU DID--
WE'RE BOTH IN THE WATER.
WHAT I DID? YOU WERE THE ONE
STANDING UP IN THE BOAT!
IF YOU WERE
WATCHING WHAT YOU WERE DOING
INSTEAD OF LOOKING AT
SOME STUPID LIGHT--
WELL, IF YOU HADN'T
PULLED ON THE OAR,
WE WOULDN'T BE
SWIMMING LIKE TUNA IN PEA SOUP!
I DO NOT
SWIM LIKE A TUNA FISH!
Joe:
WHAAA-?
Mimi:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
Piximon:
RISE AND SHINE!
EVERYBODY UP!
COME ON, PEOPLE!!
Tentomon:
PIXIMON, DO YOU KNOW WHERE
IZZY WENT--HE'S NOT IN HIS BED!
AND I CAN'T FIND MATT!
HEY, DID YOU
SEND MY BROTHER SOMEWHERE?
HE AND HIS PAL WENT TO LOOK
FOR CRESTS, ABOUT MIDNIGHT.
Tentomon:
I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
WHY WOULD IZZY LEAVE ME BEHIND?!
IT'S STRANGE--FIRST IT'S
AGUMON AND TAI LEAVING,
NOW IT'S MATT AND IZZY GONE...
EVER SINCE WE MET PIXIMON,
PEOPLE STARTED DISAPPEARING.
MAYBE NEXT,
JOE WILL TURN UP MISSING.
IT'S NOT FUNNY!
STOP FOOLING AROUND!
WHAT IF IT'S PIXIMON
MAKING EVERYONE DISAPPEAR?
COME ON, JOE, CHILL!
WE CAN TRUST PIXIMON...
CAN'T WE?
( nervously: )
YOU WOULDN'T DO ANYTHING
REALLY CRUEL, WOULD YOU?
LIKE NOT FEED US?
( disgusted: )
OH...
ATTENTION!
TRAINING WILL NOW BEGIN!
WHY DO YOU WANT TO
FIND A CREST, IZZY?
I GUESS IT'S MOSTLY
JUST BECAUSE OF KABUTERIMON.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE WHICH STAGE
HE WILL DIGIVOLVE INTO NEXT.
ISN'T THAT WHY YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR A CREST?
NO--I WANT TO USE THE CREST
TO DIGIVOLVE ME!
OH?
NOT INTO A DIGIMON, BUT TO
MAKE ME STRONGER AND SMARTER.
MAYBE LEARN SOMETHING NEW
ABOUT MYSELF--
YOU KNOW, TO REACH MY
NEXT LEVEL.
( gasps )
THE BARRIER OF THIS LAND!
DON'T TELL ME WE CAME
ALL THIS WAY FOR NOTHING!
WAIT! LOOK AT THAT GLOW!
WE MADE IT--THE CRESTS!
THE CRESTS HAVE GOT TO BE
RIGHT THERE INSIDE THE WELL!
LET'S GO!
YEAH, BUT IT'S
OUTSIDE THE WALL.
I KNOW, BUT WE'RE SO CLOSE.
I HOPE MY HAND DOESN'T MELT.
HEY! HA HA!
IT'S OKAY,
WE CAN GO THROUGH IT!
YEAH!
( grunting: )
SEE ANYTHING?
THE LIGHT'S BRIGHT DOWN HERE.
WE SHOULD TRY HOLDING OUR TAGS
UP TOWARDS THE WALL.
GOOD CALL.
WOW!
WHOA!
MAN, THIS IS HAPPENING.
WE'VE BOTH FOUND OUR CRESTS!
Gazimon:
ETEMON! WE HAVE CONTACT
IN SECTOR G-3, SIR!
THAT'S THE SECTOR WE JUST
PASSED THROUGH--TURN AROUND!!!
I CAN'T STEER WITH YOU
SHAKING ME! STOP IT!
TURN AROUND!!
STOP IT!
HA HA!
G-3 IS TYRANOMON'S TERRITORY!
SEND HIM! I LOVE A ROADIE
WITH A GOOD APPETITE!
( grunting )
( gasping )
GRRRR!!!
AAH!
Piximon:
TYRANOMON, A HUGE DIGIMON
WITH FIRE BREATH STRONG ENOU
PAH!!!!
AAH!
( growling and roaring )
OOW!
MAKING FUNNY FACES WILL NOT
DEFEAT YOUR ENEMIES.
MY BARRIER HAS BEEN BROKEN!
Tentomon:
IZZY MIGHT BE IN TROUBLE!
AND MATT!
WE'VE GOT TO HELP!
OOOOO....PAH!!
( panting )
DIDN'T I SEE THIS GUY
IN ONE OF MY NIGHTMARES?
I WISH YOU'D BE MORE CAREFUL
WHAT YOU DREAM!
Gabumon:
MATT! IZZY!
( all talking at once )
Etemon:
WELL, WELL,
ISN'T THAT NICE?
EVERYBODY'S ALL TOGETHER NOW!
YOU KNOW
I CAN'T RESIST AN AUDIENCE,
SO I GUESS IT'S SHOWTIME!
HA HA! HA HA!
( gasping and screaming )
HERE'S A LITTLE SONG I CALL
"BYE BYE, DIGIMON, BYE BYE"
♪ ( sings off-key ) ♪
OH! MY POWER'S BEEN DRAINED!
IT ZAPPED THEM!
SO NOW THEY CAN'T DIGIVOLVE!
MMMM....
PAH!
Tai:
IT'S NO USE...
THE MORE WE FIGHT IT,
THE FARTHER AWAY WE DRIFT.
Tai:
I REMEMBER THIS BRIDGE!
Boy:
UNH!
OH!
WHAT IS IT--
WHO'S THAT?
ME, BUT I...
WHAT? THAT'S YOU?
TAI! AGUMON!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
YOUR FRIENDS ARE IN TROUBLE--
COME BACK
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE!
TAI, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
( sniffling: )
I'M NEVER GONNA
LEARN HOW TO RIDE MY BIKE...
Tai:
DON'T GIVE UP--
YOU CAN'T CALL IT QUITS NOW
JUST BECAUSE OF
ONE OR TWO MISTAKES YOU MADE.
I'VE MADE PLENTY,
AND I OUGHT TO KNOW.
YOU JUST HAVE TO GET UP
AND TRY AGAIN.
OKAY, I'LL TRY.
WE CAN HOLD YOU UP,
FROM BEHIND.
SEE? YOU'RE DOING IT!
YOU'RE DOING GREAT!
I'M DOING IT ALL BY MYSELF!
I'M RIDING!
WAIT--I GET IT!
IT'S ALL ABOUT
OVERCOMING YOUR FEAR!
I WAS SO AFRAID OF YOU
DIGIVOLVING BACK INTO
SCULL GREYMON AGAIN, I LOST IT!
YOU MUST BE
A MIND READER--
THAT SAME FEAR STOPPED ME
FROM DIGIVOLVING TO GREYMON!
BUT IF WE
REALLY BELIEVE IN OURSELVES,
IT'LL BE JUST LIKE
RIDING A BIKE.
GREYMON, MY FRIEND,
I'M COMIN' BACK TO YA!
( giggling )
UMM-HMM.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY BACK!
RIGHT--TOGETHER!
OH! THEY'RE IN REAL TROUBLE!
I CAN'T WAIT FOR TAI ANY
LONGER!
HE NEEDS THIS LESSON,
BUT I'VE GOT TO ATTACK!
EVERYONE STAND BACK!PAH! PAH!
AGUMON, DIGIVOLVE!
HMM-MMM!
( celestial sounds )
AGUMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
GREYMON!!!
RRROARRRR!!!
HE DIGIVOLVED!
YEA! YEA! YEA!
NOVA BLAST!
OH!
YOU MADE IT!
HEE HEE--YEAH.
GREYMON'S PULLING
THE CABLES OUT!
GET 'EM!, GREYMON!
( grunting )
YES! YES! YES! YES! YES!
( groaning )
ARRGGHH!
Tai:
HE DID IT!
GREYMON DID IT!
Sora:
THE BLACK CABLE'S
ALL SHATTERING INTO PIECES!
ARRRRRR!!!
( all cheering )
THOSE ROTTEN KIDS BEAT ME AGAIN!
I GOTTA FIND SOMETHING
EASIER TO BEAT!
Matt:
THANK YOU, PIXIMON,
WE'VE LEARNED A LOT FROM YOU.
Joe:
YEAH, LIKE HOW TO SCRUB DOORS
AND STARVE HALF TO DEATH.
Mimi:
THAT'S JUST
JOE'S STOMACH TALKING.
Piximon:
REMEMBER, LIFE ITSELF
IS A TRAINING SESSION....
LEARN ALL YOU CAN!
RIGHT!
THEY TRULY ARE
THE DIGI-DESTINED, YEP YEP!
NO DOUBT HAVE I,
FOR THOUGH THEY ARE
SOMETIMES FOOLISH,
I HAVE SEEN
THE LOVE IN THEIR HEARTS.
WITH A LITTLE LUCK,
THEY MAY JUST SUCCEED
AND SAVE OUR DIGITAL WORLD!