Tai: LAST TIME, MATT LUCKED OUT
AND FOUND JOE IN A RESTAURANT
WHERE THESE TWO CREEPS
VEGIEMON AND DIGITAMAMON
WERE WORKING HIM LIKE A DOG
TO PAY FOR A LUNCH
HE HAD, LIKE, WEEKS AGO.
PRETTY SOON
MATT WAS SLAVING AWAY, TOO.
THE WHOLE THING WAS A SCAM
BY DEMIDEVIMON
TO KEEP THEM BOTH
THERE FOREVER.
LUCKILY, T.K. AND I
SHOWED UP JUST IN TIME.
WITH WEREGARURUMON AND MATT'S
CREST OF FRIENDSHIP GLOWING,
WE BEAT THE LITTLE BAT
AND SENT HIM AND HIS CREW
TO THE SHOWERS.
NOW WE HAD TO FIND MIMI
AND THE OTHERS,
SO WE ALL SPLIT UP AGAIN.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
THIS IS EXTREMELY PERPLEXING.
WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO FIND
GENI FOR OVER TWO MONTHS.
GOT ANY IDEAS, TENTEMON?
WE'RE WALKING IN CIRCLES.
WE COULD WALK IN SQUARES,
BUT THAT'S NOT LIKELY TO WORK.
LET'S TAKE A BREATHER,
WAIT FOR HIM TO COME TO US.
I'D PREFER
A MORE SCIENTIFIC APPROACH.
EVEN SCIENTISTS
NEED TO TAKE A BREAK.
THERE'S NO TIME TO REST,
SO STOP ASKING.
OHH.
I'M ABSOLUTELY CERTAIN
HE'S AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
I HOPE SO,
FOR MY FEET'S SAKE.
Demidevimon: THIS BETTER WORK.
[ GRUNTING ]
I HATE IT WHEN MYOTISMON
GETS ANGRY.
DEMIDEVIMON!
HA HA.
NICE DAY, HUH, BOSS?
I AM STILL WAITING FOR YOU
TO STEAL THE CREST
FROM THOSE KIDS.
I'VE GOT A SURE-FIRE WAY
TO GET THEM.
I'VE HEARD THAT BEFORE.
WOULD THIS CUTE LITTLE FACE
TELL A FIB, BOSS?
YOU'RE MYOTISMON.
I'D BE OUT OF MY HEAD
TO MAKE YOU MAD.
I'LL GIVE YOU
ONE MORE CHANCE...
WHEW.
BUT I WON'T BE SO BENEVOLENT
THE NEXT TIME.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
LOUD AND CLEAR.
IF I DON'T STEAL THOSE CRESTS,
HE'S GOING TO RAKE ME
OVER THE COALS. WAAH!
AAH!
UH-OH, THEY'RE HERE.
I'VE GOT TO HIT IT.
[ Shrieks ]
I'M CURIOUS TO KNOW
WHY GENI IS SO SECRETIVE.
I WANT TO DISCUSS THE MERITS
OF THE CREST WITH HIM.
MM-HMM.
AHA!
I LIKE THAT ABOUT YOU, IZZY.
YOU HAVE A NEVER-ENDING
THIRST FOR INFORMATION.
IT'S AMAZING YOUR BRAIN
DOESN'T EXPLODE
WITH ALL THAT KNOWLEDGE.
HOW MUCH ROOM DO YOU
HAVE LEFT IN YOUR BRAIN?
AS MUCH AS I NEED.
I WONDER WHERE GENI
COULD BE.
WITH ALL MY KNOWLEDGE,
I STILL CAN'T FIND HIM.
HMM.
LOOK, IZZY, A SIGN.
YOU MEAN FROM ABOVE?
NO, HERE
ON THE GROUND.
HOW BIZARRE. IT SAYS
"BEWARE OF FALLING SLUDGE."
UH-OH, THIS COULD GET
REAL UGLY.
AAH!
EW!
AY-YI! PLEASE TELL ME
THIS WAS JUST A DREAM.
I SAY WE GO ANYWHERE
BUT THIS WAY.
YEAH.
OH, NO, THERE'S
ANOTHER SIGN UP AHEAD.
"BOTTOMLESS SLUDGE PIT."
NOT A VERY
PLEASANT EXPERIENCE.
AAH!
OHH! I FEEL LIKE
I'VE BEEN FLUSHED!
I HOPE I NEVER SEE
ANOTHER SIGN
AS LONG AS I LIVE.
Izzy: ATTACK SLUDGE?
IMPOSSIBLE...
[ ROARING ]
OR NOT!
HOW HUMILIATING.
ATTACKED BY AN ATTACK SLUDGE.
THERE DOESN'T APPEAR TO BE
ANY OTHER PLACE FOR US TO GO.
WE'RE SURROUNDED
BY SLUDGES.
AAH!
HA HA HA HA! PERFECT!
I GOT 'EM!
THEY DON'T HAVE A CHANCE!
AAH!
THERE'S NO BOTTOM
TO THIS PIT.
WELL, THAT COULD
WORK IN OUR FAVOR.
IT'S EASIER
ON YOUR HEAD.
UNFORTUNATELY,
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
IF WE FALL ANY FARTHER,
WE'LL BE IN...
Voice: A VERY
UNPLEASANT PLACE.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
HEY, WHO SAID THAT?
WHOA! WAAH!
AAH!
Voice: DOES ANYBODY
NEED A LIFT?
HEY, WHAT ARE THESE?
Voice: I HAVE TEMPORARILY
GIVEN YOU A LIFE RAFT.
ALL THOSE THAT ARE
GREEDY FALL INTO THE PIT.
I'M NOT SURE I COMPREHEND.
WHAT ARE YOU ACCUSING US
OF BEING GREEDY FOR?
WANTING TO KNOW TOO MUCH.
STICKING YOUR NOSE
WHERE IT DOESN'T BELONG.
WHAT COULD BE WRONG
WITH GAINING KNOWLEDGE
AND INFORMATION?
SEE, YOU'RE DOING IT AGAIN.
YOU CAN'T STOP YOURSELF.
YOU'RE HEADED STRAIGHT
FOR THE PIT
IF YOU DON'T LEARN
TO CONTROL YOURSELF.
HOW COME?
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
THAT YOU'RE DOING IT!
IT'S LIKE A DISEASE
WITH YOU.
OH, WELL,
NICE KNOWING YOU.
DON'T WORRY, IZZY.
I'LL SAVE YOU.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
[ GRUNTING ]
Voice: DO YOU WANT
TO FALL IN THE PIT?
NO WAY. OF COURSE NOT.
THEN GIVE UP YOUR CURIOSITY
TO ME.
IT APPEARS I HAVE
NO OTHER CHOICE.
BUT IT'S YOUR CURIOSITY
I ADMIRE!
WHAT PROCEDURE
SHOULD I UTILIZE
TO KEEP US FROM
FALLING DOWN THIS PIT?
STOP ASKING QUESTIONS!
I WON'T, I WON'T!
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW!
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
AAH!
Izzy: I DON'T WANT TO KNOW!
WE FINALLY MADE IT OUT,
BUT WHERE ARE WE NOW?
WELCOME TO MY UNIVERSE.
I CERTAINLY HOPE
YOU ENJOY YOUR STAY HERE.
OH.
IZZY?
I'M VADEMON. I PERSONALLY
DESIGNED THIS UNIVERSE.
PRETTY NICE, DON'T YOU THINK?
JUST FOLLOW ME.
I'LL MAKE YOU
A WHOLE NEW PERSON.
Tentemon: HE SOUNDS LIKE
A REAL WEIRDO TO ME.
YOUR CURIOSITY
IS IN THIS SACK.
IT'S GARBAGE.
YOU DON'T NEED IT,
AND I DON'T WANT IT
MESSING UP MY UNIVERSE.
I JUST HATE HAVING CLUTTER.
IF IT'S NOT NEEDED,
I ZAP IT.
NOW THAT THAT'S DONE,
I WANT YOU TO READ
MY LATEST BOOK.
IT'S ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW.
"ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW,
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT."
IT HAPPENS TO BE
A BESTSELLER.
HA HA HA HA.
OH, HO HO HO.
"TO BE ONE WITH THE UNIVERSE,
YOU MUST ERASE YOUR THOUGHTS."
BUT YOUR THOUGHTS
MAKE UP WHO YOU ARE.
"BREATHE INTO YOUR THOUGHTS
UNTIL THEY DISINTEGRATE
AND SLOWLY TURN INTO MUSH."
I'VE HEARD ENOUGH!
KEEP AWAY FROM ME.
HUH?
"THE LESS YOU THINK ABOUT,
THE HAPPIER YOU'LL BE..."
SOMEONE'S TRYING
TO SEND A TRANSMISSION.
"SOON YOUR MIND
WILL SHUT DOWN,
AND YOU WILL HAVE NOTHING
LEFT TO WORRY ABOUT."
Izzy!
LOOK, IT'S TAI.
WHERE ARE YOU?
I'm home. I got your message
that you're in danger.
I'm trying to find you.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
I'M TRYING TO FIND MYSELF.
DON'T BOTHER COMING BACK
TO THE DIGIWORLD, TAI.
YOU'LL JUST CLUTTER UP
THE UNIVERSE.
Izzy!
TAI'S RISKING HIS LIFE
TO SAVE YOU, IZZY.
OH, WELL.
HE'S YOUR FRIEND.
"INDIFFERENCE IS THE KEY
TO SUCCESS."
THE IZZY I KNEW
IS NO MORE.
♪ OH, DO DO DO DO ♪
HO HO HO HO HO.
HA HA HA HA HA HA.
I'VE GOT A WAREHOUSE
FULL OF CURIOSITIES
AND OTHER CASTAWAY ITEMS,
AND ALL OF THEM
ARE FOR SALE.
THERE'S ALWAYS SOMEONE
WHO WANTS TO BUY JUNK,
AND I KNOW THE SALESMAN
WHO CAN GIVE THEM A BARGAIN.
VADEMON -- CURIOSITY SALESMAN
EXTRAORDINAIRE.
A PENNY FOR YOUR THOUGHTS
AND A NICKEL FOR YOUR FEARS.
HMM.
HA HA!
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
JUST A MINUTE.
I'LL BE RIGHT WITH YOU.
WELL, HAVE I GOT A BARGAIN
FOR YOU.
I HOPE SO.
I'M RUNNING A SALE
RIGHT NOW.
DREAMS AND CURIOSITIES
ARE AT BOTTOM LINE PRICES.
IT'S A STEAL --
HUH?
DID ANYONE IN THIS PICTURE
TUMBLE INTO YOUR UNIVERSE?
WHY, YES, THEY DID.
PERFECT.
YOU MUST BE IN THE MARKET
FOR THE CURIOSITIES.
I'LL FETCH THEM
FOR YOU.
AY.
AAH!
THEY'RE VERY FRESH.
FOR BRAIN GARBAGE,
THIS IS THE PLACE.
I'M LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING ELSE.
DON'T TRY TO GIVE ME
A HARD TIME,
OR I'LL GET MAD.
I WANT THIS.
THE KID IN THE PICTURE
WAS CARRYING A TAG
AND A CREST WITH HIM.
THAT'S NOT SOMETHING
I ORDINARILY CARRY.
VERY EXPENSIVE.
HMM. HOW ABOUT I TRADE HIM
FOR SOME OF MY CURIOSITY?
HMM?
[ Thinking ] HE MUST HAVE
A MOUNTAIN OF CURIOUS THOUGHTS.
OOH.
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY,
VADEMON,
IS IT A DEAL OR NOT?
IT CERTAINLY IS.
HOO HOO HOO.
I CAN TELL BY LOOKING AT YOU
THAT YOU'RE A DIGIMON
WITH ENOUGH WACKY THOUGHTS
TO MAKE ME A FORTUNE.
Izzy: A...
B...
C...
D...
E...
F...
G...
H...
IZZY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M PREPARING MY BRAIN WAVES
BY FOCUSING ON SOME
BASIC FUNDAMENTALS,
SO I WOULD RATHER
YOU DID NOT DISTURB ME.
I...
J...
K...
L...
M...
N...
THERE'S SOMETHING
I FORGOT TO MENTION TO YOU.
OH, YES? WHAT?
IN ORDER TO FULLY
IMPROVE YOURSELF,
YOU MUST THROW AWAY POSSESSIONS
THAT ARE EXCESS BAGGAGE.
SUCH AS?
JUST ABOUT EVERYTHING
EXCEPT YOUR CLOTHES.
OF COURSE.
IZZY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS IS EXPENDABLE.
HA HA HA HA HA HA HA.
HAVE YOU GONE BANANAS?
YOU CAN'T THROW THOSE AWAY.
HMM, WHAT A NICE-LOOKING
TRINKET.
GIVE BACK THAT TAG AND CREST,
YOU POOR EXCUSE FOR A DIGIMON!
BACK OFF, BUG.
AAH!
IZZY!
FORGET ABOUT HIM.
GET BACK TO YOUR TRAINING.
YES. O...
P...
Q...
R...
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
T...
U...
V...
W...
X...
AAH!
SO SORRY
TO MAKE YOU WAIT.
YEAH! ALL RIGHT.
GIVE ME THE GOODS!
WAIT. DON'T YOU RECALL
THE DEAL THAT WE MADE?
I WANT A PIECE
OF YOUR BRAIN.
I'M GOING TO CRANK OUT
SOME OF MY THOUGHTS.
I'M TRYING, BUT IT'S HARD
TO GET THEM OUT OF MY HEAD.
[ GRUNTING ]
COME ON, HURRY UP.
I'LL HELP.
AAH!
OHH.
E...
F...
G...
I'VE LOST HIM.
H...
I...
J...
I-I HAVE NO ENERGY LEFT.
RRR.
HUH?
MOTEMON.
PABU.
PABUMON?
[ Crying ] PABU, PABU, PABU.
I TOLD YOU NOT TO BOTHER ME
WHEN I'M MEDITATING!
PABU, PABU.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
WHO I AM ALREADY, IZZY?
WHO YOU ARE?
TRY TO REMEMBER.
TRY.
UHH...HUH?
I JUST WANT TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT THE DIGIWORLD REALLY IS.
CAN'T REMEMBER.
AAH!
Tentemon: HOLD ON, IZZY,
AND DON'T LET GO
OF YOUR CURIOSITY.
Izzy: THIS IS MERELY
SCIENTIFIC SPECULATION,
BUT I BELIEVE I'VE STUMBLED
ONTO SOMETHING MORE
MORE THAN JUST A SIMPLE
COMPUTER GAME.
NO!
[ GRUNTING ]
OH!
PABU, PABU.
PLEASE DON'T CRY,
PABUMON.
OH, SORRY.
PABU.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO MAKE YOU DEDIGEVOLVE.
PABU, PABU.
Vademon: YOU LIED!
YOU'RE NOTHING
BUT A WEASEL-MON.
Demidevimon: DON'T GET
BENT OUT OF SHAPE!
I'M GOING TO
GET IN BIG TROUBLE.
Vademon: IT'S NOT MY CONCERN,
YOU PESKY PIPSQUEAK.
BEAT IT, PAL.
MYOTISMON WILL
PULL MY FEATHERS OUT
IF I DON'T BRING HIM
THAT TAG AND CREST.
YOU GOT YOURSELF INTO THIS,
YOU CAN GET YOURSELF OUT.
PLEASE, I'M BEGGING YOU.
HE'S A BIG BRUTE.
Vademon: BACK OFF!
I'M MIXED UP
BECAUSE MY CURIOSITY'S GONE,
BUT I BELIEVE SOMEHOW
I'VE BEEN TRICKED,
SO I MUST IMPLEMENT
A PLAN TO GET IT BACK.
UNFORTUNATELY, ALL I'M
COMING UP WITH IS A BIG ZERO.
PABU, PABU.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME WAY
I CAN GET MY CURIOSITY
OUT OF THERE,
BUT I CAN'T FIGURE OUT HOW.
GET OUT!
FORGET IT!
NO, IT'S NOT.
IT'S MINE.
Vademon: YOU WANT TO BET?
Demidevimon: HAND IT OVER.
NOW YOU'VE
REALLY GOT ME MAD.
HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
HE'S STOLEN
THE TAG AND CREST!
COME BACK HERE!
WHERE'D HE COME FROM?
PABUMON, OVER HERE!
Demidevimon: STOP!
HURRY!
THEY TRICKED US!
Vademon: OHH!
Demidevimon: AAH!
Together: [ GROANING ]
THAT'S GOOD WORK, PABUMON.
YOU GOT THE CREST.
PABU, PABU.
UH, YOU WANT ME
TO FOLLOW YOU?
OPEN UP!
Demidevimon: MYOTISMON
WILL HAVE ME FOR LUNCH!
PRODIGIOUS!
YOU FOUND MY CURIOSITY.
IT WAS A MISTAKE
TO GIVE IT UP.
I'M SORRY I JUST
TOSSED IT AWAY.
CURIOSITY IS ESSENTIAL.
PABU, PABU.
I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO CONCENTRATE.
I HOPE IT TRANSFERS.
COME BACK IN MY HEART.
HMM.
HA! NOW YOU'RE GOING TO
PAY FOR THIS!
AAH!
PABU!
[ PANTING ]
AAH!
PABUMON, IT'S TIME
FOR YOU TO DIGEVOLVE!
MOTEMON.
MOTEMON!
AAH!
OHH! WAAH!
TENTEMON!
WHOA!
TENTEMON! AAH!
IZZY, BE CAREFUL!
TENTEMON, DIGEVOLVE TO...
KABUTERIMON!
[ GASPS ]
Both: WHOA!
WHAT I NEED
IS SOME PEST CONTROL.
TOODLE-OO!
[ ROARING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
KABUTERIMON!
SORRY, BUT I'VE NEVER
BEEN VERY PARTIAL
TO VERMIN DIGIMON.
HA HA HA HA!
GET UP!
YOU'VE GOT TO DIGEVOLVE!
KABUTERIMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
MEGAKABUTERIMON!
GRR!
HORN BUSTER!
[ GROWLS AND ROARS ]
KABUTERIMON WAS SUCCESSFUL.
HE DIGEVOLVED
TO ULTIMATE MEGAKABUTERIMON.
LET'S SEE IF YOU
CAN TAKE HIM ON, VADEMON.
I HAVE A SURPRISE
FOR HIM, TOO.
TOODLE-OO!
HOO, HOO, HOO!
[ ROARS ]
GO, MEGAKABUTERIMON!
NOTHING LIKE
A SPEEDING PLANET
TO GIVE THEM
THE ULTIMATE HEADACHE.
AH-HA HA HA HA!
HUH?
AAH!
ALL RIGHT!
THANKS, MEGAKABUTERIMON!
[ GASPING ]
IZZY, WAKE UP.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
OHH.
I WAS SO WORRIED.
I'M FINE.
OHH. I'M SO TIRED
I CAN BARELY STAND UP.
OH, I'M SORRY.
OH, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW.
IZZY, AWESOME!
YOU MADE IT BACK!
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE BACK.
YEAH, AND WE'RE BUSHED.
HOW'S IT GOING?
BETTER NOW.
TELL US WHAT HAPPENED.
YEAH, WE THOUGHT YOU
WERE A DIGI-GONER.
IZZY WAS TAKING
A SELF-IMPROVEMENT CLASS.
I IMPROVED SO MUCH
I FLUNKED RIGHT OUT.
HELLO, KIDS.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
IT'S GENI.
Geni: THE CONNECTION BETWEEN
THE WORLDS IS STILL DAMAGED.
YOU'LL HAVE TO STAY LONGER.
I'VE COLLECTED SOME INFORMATION
ABOUT THE DIGITAL WORLD
THAT YOU'LL BE ABLE TO USE.
TAKE A LOOK AT THE DIGIMON FILE.
IT'LL TELL YOU
ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW.
I WONDER IF THERE'S
ANYONE WE KNOW IN HERE.
I'VE JUST DOWNLOADED
MY FAVORITE --
MEGAKABUTERIMON.
YEAH, I'M A COOL DUDE.
A FUNNY THING HAPPENED TO ME
ON THE WAY TO VADEMON'S.
PREPARE TO FACE
THE CONSEQUENCES!
I HATE THIS PART!
QUIET!
YOU HAD YOUR CHANCE.
OHH!
DON'T MAKE ME SIT
IN THIS TREE ALL NIGHT.
AAH!
I'M AFRAID OF HEIGHTS!
CAN I AT LEAST HAVE
SOME MILK AND COOKIES?