Joe: PIXIMON
WAS UNABLE TO FIGHT OFF
ALL OF THE DARK MASTERS,
BUT WE WERE GRATEFUL TO HIM
AND HIS NOBLE DEFEAT.
SOMETIME LATER,
WE WERE ON OUR WAY
TO WHAT WE THOUGHT
WAS A BEACH PICNIC,
BUT IT TURNED OUT TO BE A TRAP
SET UP BY SCORPIOMON.
WITH MOST OF THE GROUP
UNCONSCIOUS,
IT WAS UP TO US
TO RESCUE THEM.
ZUDOMON AND LILLYMON ALLOWED US
TO GET THE GANG OUT OF THE HUT
JUST AS METAL SEADRAMON
WAS BLASTING IT INTO RUBBLE.
WE ESCAPED INTO THE OCEAN
ON ZUDOMON'S BACK...
AT LEAST WE THOUGHT
WE GOT AWAY.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
RIVER OF POWER!
OHH!
OW!
YOU'RE FINISHED,
YOU UPSTART DIGIDESTINED!
IN A WORD, YOU'RE SUNK!
HUH?
WHO IS THAT?
IT'S WHAMON!
[ ROARS ]
AAH!
AH. OHH.
COME ON, EVERYBODY.
I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D WANT TO BE FISH FOOD,
BUT WE'LL BE SAFE IN HERE.
Izzy: TECHNICALLY
IT'S A MAMMAL.
[ GROWLS ]
AH! YOU ESCAPE THIS TIME,
BUT YOU'VE ESCAPED
FOR THE LAST TIME.
WHY DID WHAMON STICK
HIS SPOUT IN MY BUSINESS
AND SAVE THE DIGIDESTINED?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
DIVERMON?
WE JUST CAME UP
FOR A LITTLE AIR.
Metal Seadramon:
THOSE DIVERMON!
IF IT WASN'T FOR
THEIR STRIKING FISH ATTACK,
THEY'D BE USELESS TO ME.
NO MATTER.
WHEREVER THOSE KIDS
TRY TO HIDE, I'LL FIND THEM.
I RULE THIS OCEAN
WITH AN IRON HAND, AN IRON TAIL,
AND AN IRON EVERYTHING,
FOR THAT MATTER.
I'LL CATCH THEM
EVEN WITH WHAMON ON THEIR SIDE.
WELL, DON'T JUST SIT THERE
TREADING WATER.
I TOLD YOU
TO GO FIND THOSE KIDS!
Both: AYE-AYE, SIR.
[ GROWLS ]
Tai: THANKS FOR SAVING US,
WHAMON.
AH, DON'T MENTION IT.
NO, SERIOUSLY,
DON'T MENTION IT.
I DON'T WANT IT
TO GET AROUND.
HEY, GUYS,
WE STILL HAVE A PROBLEM.
HOW ARE WE GOING TO BE ABLE
TO DEFEAT THE DARK MASTERS?
I WONDER HOW THEY TOOK OVER
THE DIGITAL WORLD
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
DO YOU REMEMBER, WHAMON?
Whamon: OF COURSE
I REMEMBER WHAMON.
BIG FELLA. SNAPPY DRESSER.
OH, YOU MEAN
THE DARK MASTERS.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
ALL THE DETAILS,
BUT SOON AFTER THE DIGITAL WORLD
BEGAN TO WARP,
METAL SEADRAMON BEGAN
TO TAKE OVER THE OCEAN.
Tai: DARN!
Whamon: OW.
Tai: OH, SORRY, WHAMON.
TAI, DON'T GET UPSET.
WE'LL FIX THINGS.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE'LL DO IT.
WE'VE DONE IT BEFORE,
HAVEN'T WE?
All: YEAH!
Whamon: THAT'S THE ATTITUDE.
I'LL FIND
A SAFE PLACE FOR YOU
OUTSIDE
OF METAL SEADRAMON'S REACH,
EVEN IF I HAVE TO SWIM
TO THE FAR CORNERS
OF THE OCEAN.
BY THE WAY, DID I MENTION
I CHARGE BY THE MILE?
[ GROWLS ]
All: AAH!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
Gatomon: ♪ CATS LAND
ON THEIR FEET ♪
♪ BUT WE STILL
NEED TO EAT ♪
♪ IT'S GATOMON'S WISH
FOR SOME FRESH FLYING FISH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M A KITTY,
A DIGI-KITTY ♪
MEOW!
All: OH!
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
MEOW.
Palmon: THAT'S GREAT,
GATOMON,
BUT THE REST OF US
HAVE TO EAT, TOO.
STAND ASIDE AND WATCH
HOW A PRO DOES IT.
[ HUMMING ]
POISON IVY!
All: WHOA!
AH!
DINNER IS SERVED.
WHY'D YOU
STOP PLAYING, MATT?
OH, THAT SONG
IS JUST TOO DEPRESSING.
IT ALWAYS
GIVES ME THE BLUES.
[ SIGHS ]
BESIDES,
I CAN'T STOP THINKING
ABOUT THE DARK MASTERS.
THEY'RE DIFFERENT
THAN ANY DIGIMON
WE'VE EVER FACED BEFORE.
WELL, I'VE ANALYZED
THE SITUATION,
AND I BELIEVE
WE CAN DEFEAT THEM
WITH WARGREYMON.
HUH?
HE'S A DRAMON DESTROYER.
DRAMON DESTROYER?
TRY SPEAKING ENGLISH.
WELL, YOU SEE, THE WEAPONS
ON WARGREYMON'S ARMS
ARE THE KEY.
THEY'RE ESPECIALLY EFFECTIVE
AGAINST DRAMON-TYPE DIGIMON.
HENCE THE PHRASE
"DRAMON DESTROYER."
WITH THESE DEVICES,
WE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO DEFEAT THE DARK MASTERS.
IZZY, YOU'RE A GENIUS.
DRAMON DESTROYER, HUH?
AGUMON, YOU'RE GOING TO EAT
THOSE DRAMON ALIVE.
All: OH! EW!
Boys: HUH?
THAT'S NOT
WHAT I HAD IN MIND.
FISHES, LEARN ANYTHING NEW
IN SCHOOL?
WE LEARNED DIVERMON
ARE IN THE AREA.
WHAT?
WAAH!
WHAA!
Hey, guys,
we got trouble.
All: HUH? OH.
I CAUGHT A WHOPPER. LOOK.
[ MOANS ]
DIVERMON
ARE HEADED THIS WAY!
AAH!
Mimi: NOT DIVERMON.
ANYTHING BUT DIVERMON.
BY THE WAY,
WHAT ARE DIVERMON?
Whamon: OH, THOSE ARE
METAL SEADRAMON'S HENCHMEN.
IT SEEMS THE FISH
HAVE SEEN THEM
ABOUT 200 MILES BEHIND US.
All: HUH?
T.K.: WHAT ARE WE
GOING TO DO?
Whamon: WELL,
WE CAN'T STAY HERE.
THEY'LL FIND US TOO EASILY.
I'M GOING TO DIVE.
QUICK, EVERYONE GET INSIDE ME.
DON'T MIND THE SMELL.
I HAD FISH FOR LUNCH.
All: EW!
RED LEADER TO BLUE LEADER.
AREAS 13 THROUGH 18
ARE CLEAR.
GOLD LEADER TO BLUE LEADER.
AREAS 23 AND 24
ARE CLEAR, TOO.
PHIL, SID, HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU GUYS?
THERE ARE JUST
THREE OF US.
YOU CAN CALL ME JIM.
WOULD YOU GUYS
KNOCK IT OFF?
DO YOU SMELL SOMETHING?
THERE'S THE SCENT
OF DIGIDESTINED
IN THE CURRENT.
THAT OR THERE'S A BAD PATCH
OF SEAWEED AROUND HERE.
PEUW.
THIS IS
MY MOMENT TO SHINE.
DOES MY HAIR
LOOK ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
YOU DIGIDESTINED FOOLS!
YOU CAN SWIM,
BUT YOU CAN'T HIDE.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
WHAT'S THAT NOISE?
I WAS TAKING A CATNAP,
AND IT WOKE ME UP.
Izzy: I'LL EXPLAIN LATER.
OH, COME ON.
YOU THINK I'M TOO BRAINLESS
TO UNDERSTAND?
YES, BUT I'LL
TELL YOU ANYWAY.
CHECK IT OUT.
Mimi: WHAT DID
YOU DO, IZZY?
Sora: WHAT A COOL
SCREEN SAVER.
Izzy: IT'S NOT
A SCREEN SAVER.
WHAT IS IT THEN?
I CONNECTED
TO WHAMON'S HARD DRIVE
AND RE-ROUTED
ALL HIS SENSORY INFORMATION
TO MY COMPUTER.
IN OTHER WORDS,
WHAT YOU'RE SEEING ON SCREEN
IS EXACTLY WHAT WHAMON
IS LOOKING AT RIGHT NOW.
Matt: COOL!
LIKE A SUBMARINE.
OH, BOY!
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO GO ON A SUBMARINE.
Joe: I THINK SHE'S BEEN
OUT TO SEA A LITTLE TOO LONG.
[ MIMI LAUGHS HYSTERICALLY ]
YEAH,
I HATE SQUARE DANCING.
WHAT'S WRONG, KARI?
IT'S MY EARS.
THEY'RE STARTING TO HURT.
MIMI, STOP. BE QUIET.
OH! HEY, YOU KNOW,
MY EARS HURT A LITTLE, TOO.
Joe: ME TOO.
Gabumon: MY EARS!
Whamon: SORRY.
I DOVE A LITTLE TOO FAST.
I'LL FIX THE PRESSURE NOW.
HOLD ON.
[ MOANS ]
[ BURPS ]
AHH.
THAT'S BETTER.
WELL, I GUESS
THAT'S ONE WAY
TO EQUALIZE
THE GAS PRESSURE.
BY THE WAY,
YOU'RE EXCUSED.
Biyomon:
WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
HUH?
IT'S GETTING LOUDER.
Izzy: EVERYONE BE QUIET.
Tentomon:
SOUNDS LIKE DIVERMON!
[ GASP ]
OH.
SOUNDS LIKE
THEY'VE PASSED US.
Whamon: WE'RE NOT
OUT OF DANGER YET.
WE'LL HAVE TO BE QUIET
A LITTLE LONGER.
EH?
OVER THERE!
HEY, IT'S WHAMON!
All: AAH!
OH, NO! THEY FOUND US.
RED LEADER, THIS IS --
I MEAN, THIS IS PHIL.
I FOUND WHAMON.
HE'S IN AREA 51
ON THE OCEAN FLOOR.
GREAT!
KEEP AN EYE ON HIM.
I'LL TELL THE BOSS,
AND HE CAN TELL
METAL SEADRAMON.
GOOD NEWS!
WE FOUND WHAMON.
[ ROARS ]
WHAT DO WE DO NOW,
O MASTER OF THE OCEAN?
ATTACK!
STRIKING FISH!
WATCH OUT!
THE DIVERMON
ARE ATTACKING.
HANG ON, EVERYONE.
I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
All: AAH!
Phil: WHERE DID ALL
THOSE BUBBLES COME FROM?
GEE, I COULDN'T SEE
WHERE I WAS AIMING.
HUH? UH-OH.
YOU'RE SQUEEZING ME
TOO HARD.
MATT, YOU'RE
SQUEEZING ME TOO HARD.
SORRY. I GUESS WE'RE ALL
A LITTLE SCARED.
AH! I HATE THIS.
WE'RE STUCK IN HERE
AND CAN'T FIGHT.
ACCORDING
TO THE AUDIO SENSORS,
THERE ARE THREE MORE
BEHIND US.
Sora: WHAT IS IT, WHAMON?
Whamon: IT'S THE ENEMY.
DON'T LET THEM GET AWAY.
OH, THEY'RE
GAINING ON US!
THAT'S IT!
I'M TIRED OF RUNNING.
COME ON, WHAMON. LET'S GO UP
TO THE SURFACE AND FIGHT.
Whamon: LET ME TRY
ONE MORE THING.
HOPEFULLY IT'LL WORK.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
HOPEFULLY IT'LL WORK?
Mimi: THAT'S WHAT THE CAPTAIN
OF THE TITANIC SAID.
STRIKING FISH!
AND WHAT IF IT DOESN'T WORK?
WHAT'S PLAN "B?"
Tai: I STILL THINK
WE SHOULD TURN AND FIGHT.
I HOPE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING, WHAMON.
WHAT'S HE TRYING TO DO?
WHAMON MUST BE CRAZY
TRYING TO ESCAPE
INTO SUCH A NARROW SPACE.
STAY WITH HIM
NO MATTER WHAT.
[ ROARS ]
YOU, IN THE BIG WHALE,
PULL OVER.
IT'S NO USE.
WE'VE GOT YOU TRAPPED.
OH, NO! THEY'LL CATCH US!
EYAH!
Both: NO!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
AAH!
HMM?
[ BABBLING AND CRYING ]
TOUGH BREAK.
OH, THAT'S GOT TO HURT.
PRODIGIOUS! THEY CAN'T
TAKE THE WATER PRESSURE.
THAT WAS WHAMON'S PLAN
ALL ALONG.
Gomamon: WHAMON IS BUILT
TO HANDLE PRESSURE,
UNLIKE SOME OF US.
Joe: WELL, FORGIVE ME
FOR NOT BEING A WHALE.
[ EVERYONE LAUGHS ]
BOY, THAT WAS CLOSE.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD
THIS KIND OF HIDDEN ATTACK.
THIS IS GREAT, BUT WHAT
ARE WE GOING TO DO NOW?
Sora: YEAH, WE CAN'T STAY
AT THE BOTTOM FOREVER.
Izzy: I'VE GOT IT.
KARI, COME OVER HERE
FOR A MOMENT.
[ WHISPERS ]
HUH?
AH. RIGHT.
TA-DA!
READY?
YOU CAN DO IT.
[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
[ BLOWS WHISTLE ]
All: HUH?
[ GROUP GASPS ]
[ KARI GRUNTS ]
YEAH! WE DID IT, KARI.
[ PANTS ]
THANKS FOR THE HELP.
SURE.
THE WHISTLE
WAS SORT OF LIKE SONAR.
WE USED THE REVERBERATIONS
OF THE SOUND
TO FIND A TUNNEL,
AND THERE'S ONE UP AHEAD
THAT SHOULD LEAD US TO LAND.
Tai: ISN'T THAT GREAT,
WHAMON?
Whamon: WHAT?
Tai: I SAID, ISN'T THAT GREAT?
Whamon: I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
SOMEONE WAS WHISTLING IN MY EAR.
THERE'S A TUNNEL.
IT SHOULD LEAD US TO LAND.
THOSE FOOLS THINK
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE THEY'RE HEADED.
THEY'RE EASIER TO FIGURE OUT
THAN A 2-PIECE JIGSAW PUZZLE.
ENJOY PLAYING SUBMARINE
WHILE YOU CAN.
[ ROARS ]
Girls: WOW! PRETTY!
AHA!
Matt: A TUNNEL?
YAY! WE'RE SAVED.
I'VE GOT TO GET CHANGED.
HUH?
HUG!
All: AAH!
NOT AGAIN.
HOW CAN THOSE FISH HEADS
BE BACK?
Whamon: THEY'RE NOT.
BE CAREFUL, EVERYONE.
IT'S METAL SEADRAMON.
[ ROARS ]
WHOA.
[ GROWLS ]
All: WHOA!
Tai: IS EVERYBODY OKAY?
Izzy: WHERE -- WHERE ARE WE?
THE SUN'S SO BRIGHT.
SMELL THAT. FRESH AIR.
I FEEL I'VE BEEN
UNDERWATER SO LONG,
I MIGHT NEVER TAKE
A BATH AGAIN.
[ EVERYONE LAUGHS ]
Metal Seadramon: YOU MIND
TELLING ME WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
All: AAH!
[ GROWLS ]
IT'S METAL SEADRAMON.
HOW CAN IT BE?
IT WAS ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE YOU CAME UP FOR AIR.
NOW YOU'RE GOING DOWN
WITH THE SHIP!
Whamon: EVERYONE HOLD ON!
TIDAL WAVE!
AAH!
SHOULD I?
SURE, GO FOR IT.
WHILE AGUMON
GETS THEIR ATTENTION,
LET'S CROSS TO THE SHORE
AND PREPARE OURSELVES
FOR BATTLE.
AYE-AYE.
GOMAMON AND I
WILL STAY HERE
AND BRING UP THE REAR.
JOE, DON'T BE SUCH A COWARD.
AGUMON!
HERE I GO.
AGUMON WARP-DIGEVOLVE TO...
WARGREYMON!
[ ROARS ]
[ GROWLS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT WAS THAT, A LOVE TAP?
I'M MADE
OF CHROMEDIGIZOID, TOO.
YOU CAN'T HURT
ME THAT EASILY.
WHAMON,
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING,
BUT YOU CAN LEAVE
THE REST TO US.
WHAT, NO TIP?
Matt: HURRY
AND GET OUT OF HERE.
YOU'RE AN EASY TARGET.
YOU'RE JUST TOO BIG.
ARE YOU CALLING ME FAT?
I'M JUST BIG-BONED.
STRIKING FISH!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
AH! EE! OOH!
AH! EE! OOH! AH!
IKKAKUMON, QUICK --
DIGEVOLVE.
IKKAKUMON, DIGEVOLVE TO...
ZUDOMON!
[ GROWLS ]
VULCAN'S HAMMER!
RIVER OF POWER!
TERRA FORCE!
GOT YOU!
Wargreymon: NO!
WARGREYMON!
BIG TROUBLE.
WARGREYMON'S
AT A HUGE DISADVANTAGE
IN THE WATER.
Wargreymon: VULCAN'S HAMMER!
Wargreymon and Metal Seadramon:
AAH!
OH, BOY.
IS EVERYBODY OKAY?
[ ROARS ]
WARGREYMON!
I CAN'T WATCH.
Metal Seadramon: I'M TIRED
OF PLAYING AROUND WITH YOU,
WARGREYMON.
SAY GOODBYE!
IS THIS REALLY THE END
FOR WARGREYMON?
WILL THE DIGIDESTINED
EVER DEFEAT THE DARK MASTERS?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."