Mimi: JOE AND I
WERE TIRED OF THE FIGHTING,
SO WE DECIDED
TO SIT ONE OUT.
WE SAW WHAT LOOKED LIKE
A GIANT MEATBALL
FALL OUT OF THE SKY.
TURNS OUT IT WAS ETEMON,
EXCEPT SHINIER.
HE WAS NOW METAL ETEMON,
LOOKING FOR REVENGE.
THE OTHER KIDS WERE ABLE TO GET
INSIDE PUPPETMON'S MANSION,
AND WITH THE HELP
OF HIS UNHAPPY GUARDS,
USE SOME OF HIS TOYS
AGAINST HIM.
JOE AND I FOUND OGREMON,
WHO'D BEEN WOUNDED.
WHEN WE FIXED HIM UP,
HE COULDN'T BELIEVE WE
WERE BEING SO NICE TO HIM.
THINGS SEEMED FAIRLY QUIET
FOR A CHANGE.
OF COURSE, QUIET NEVER
LAST LONGS HERE.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
GRRR!
WHO'S THAT?
HEY, DON'T YOU
COME ANY CLOSER.
WAIT, I WON'T HURT YOU.
DO WE BELIEVE YOU?
HE SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
GRRR.
WAIT, I DON'T TRUST HIM.
Metal Etemon: DON'T GIVE ME
ANY JIVE, BABY.
COME OUT,
WHEREVER YOU ARE.
I'LL EXPLAIN
EVERYTHING LATER.
RIGHT NOW, WE NEED
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
AAH!
HEY, WAIT UP!
DON'T LEAVE ME HERE
WITH THIS
WHACKED-OUT MONKEY.
UHH!
SUPREME! I'M FIRED UP AND READY
TO GO ON A MEAN STREAK.
SLOW DOWN, YOU 4-FOOTED
GIANT FURBALL!
Mimi: THIS IS MORE CONVENIENT
THAN WAITING FOR A TAXI.
Joe: IF I'D KNOWN
WE WERE GOING TO GO RIDING,
I'D HAVE WORN LONG PANTS.
ME, TOO.
THIS PLACE DOESN'T
LOOK VERY LIVELY.
IT'S KIND OF SPOOKY.
LOOK UP THERE!
I THINK
I'M GOING TO BARF.
THAT'S THE RESTAURANT
WHERE THEY MADE ME
WORK LIKE A SLAVE.
I'M TRYING TO GET
THAT SMELL OUT.
BUT THIS IS ALL WRONG.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
NEAR A LAKE.
EVERYTHING'S CHANGED.
HURRY, WE'D BETTER FIND SHELTER.
Joe: THIS PLACE
IS DEPRESSING.
Mimi: THERE'S NOT EVEN
A CLEAN CHAIR TO SIT ON.
HUH?
AAH!
LEOMON, YOU ARE NOT GOING
TO BELIEVE WHAT YOU MISSED.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S YOU!
I AM TRULY HAPPY
TO HAVE FINALLY RETURNED
AND HELP MY FRIENDS.
YOU DIGIVOLVED.
A LOT HAS HAPPENED TO ME
SINCE BEING SET FREE
OF THE BLACK GEARS
AND THEIR EVIL POWER.
BEING EXPOSED
TO THE DIGIVICE
HAS NOW ENABLED ME
TO DIGIVOLVE,
BUT THERE'S ONE PROBLEM --
I AM UNABLE TO CONTROL IT.
I HAVEN'T LEARNED
THE SECRET YET.
IT'S ALL STILL NEW TO ME.
WHAT MAKES YOU SPECIAL,
YOU DOGGIE CHEW TOY?
LET'S JUST SEE HOW MANY LIVES
YOU HAVE LEFT, HUH?
GRRR, GRRR, GRRR!
SCAREDY-CAT! UHH! UHH!
UHH! OHH!
THERE IS NOTHING MORE
PATHETIC THAN A WHINER.
CLEARLY YOU DON'T DESERVE
TO BE CALLED A DIGIMON.
[ GROANS ]
Both: AAH!
AAH!
Both: HUH?
WHO'S IN THERE?
SHOW YOURSELF!
THE LAST THING WE WANT
IS TO CAUSE TROUBLE!
OH, PALMON, LOOK.
THEY DELIVERED
THE TRIPLE HOT FUDGE SUNDAE.
HUH? WOW, THE PRINCESS!
WHAT LUCK!
HUH?
PRINCESS MIMI!
YIPPEE!
HA HA HA! YAHOO!
TAKE THAT!
HA HA HA HA HA!
HERE HE COMES!
OH, NO!
HE'S MAD!
WELL, WE ARE
SHOOTING AT HIM.
I BET THEY DON'T
INVITE PUPPETMON
TO THEIR
BIRTHDAY PARTIES.
IT'S A GOOD THING THEY'RE
RELEASING THEIR HOSTILITY.
GET OUT NOW!
Both: WAH!
WHOA!
YOU GUYS KNOW
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED UPSTAIRS!
MY ROOM IS OFF-LIMITS!
PLUS, I HATE SHARING
MY TOYS!
YOU NEED TO LEARN A LITTLE
MORE ABOUT GOOD MANNERS.
WE'RE NOT HURTING ANYTHING,
EXCEPT MAYBE YOU.
WE'VE HAD IT WITH YOU,
PUPPETMON.
YOU'RE TOAST!
SO NOW YOU WANT
TO PLAY, HUH?
HOW ABOUT A GAME
OF FOLLOW THE LEADER?
COME BACK HERE,
YOU PUNY TOOTHPICK!
YOU PLAY WITH US,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE!
[ GASPS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
HUH? IT'S A TRICK.
I DON'T LIKE VEGETABLES.
HA HA HA!
LOOK, LOOK, PUNK!
I HAVE FRIENDS AFTER ALL!
THE PROBLEM IS
THEY DON'T LIKE YOU!
HA HA HA HA!
AND WHAT THEY DON'T LIKE,
THEY DESTROY.
All: YEAH, BOSS!
Tai: REDVEGGIEMON HAVE
EXTREMELY VOLATILE TEMPERS.
THAT'S WHY THEIR FACES
ARE ALWAYS RED.
NOT EXACTLY THE FRIENDLY TYPE.
[ GROWLING ]
IT'S TIME TO DO
SOME WEED WHACKING.
HOW COME YOU TWO WERE HIDING?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR PALACE?
THE PALACE WAS
COMPLETELY DESTROYED
BY THOSE
CREEPY DARK MASTERS.
YEAH, IT WAS HORRIBLE.
THEY ATTACKED
JUST FOR THE FUN OF IT.
WE WERE ALL SEPARATED,
AND WE'VE BEEN HIDING
EVER SINCE.
HOW AWFUL.
THOSE GUYS MAKE ME SICK.
WHO DO THEY THINK
THEY ARE, ANYWAY,
PICKING ON POOR,
DEFENSELESS DIGIMON?
I MEAN, IS THAT FAIR?
THE DARK MASTERS
HAVE TO BE STOPPED
IF WE EXPECT TO SURVIVE.
I'VE SPENT ALL THIS TIME
SEARCHING FOR YOU,
BUT IT HASN'T BEEN EASY.
THE DARK MASTERS
HAVE SEEN TO THAT.
YOU TWO HAVE THE POWER
TO DEFEAT THOSE BEASTS,
BUT YOU MUST WORK TOGETHER
AND JOIN FORCES
WITH THE OTHER DIGIDESTINED.
ONLY THEN WILL YOU SUCCEED.
ARE YOU SAYING
WE WASTED OUR TIME
FIGHTING EVERYONE ELSE?
I MEAN, I COULD HAVE STAINED
MY CLOTHES WITH PERSPIRATION.
HA HA HA!
LISTEN, GIRLIE,
IF YOU WOULD'VE FOUGHT
THOSE GUYS AT THE START,
YOU WOULD'VE BROKEN
WAY MORE THAN JUST A SWEAT.
MAYBE, BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE GOOD DIGIMON ON FILE ISLAND
THAT SACRIFICED
THEMSELVES TO HELP US?
[ CRYING ]
MIMI --
Leomon: THIS IS TRUE.
I THINK YOU WERE BROUGHT
TO FILE ISLAND
TO PROVE THAT YOU WERE CAPABLE
OF WORKING AS A TEAM,
TO MAKE SURE
YOU WERE THE DIGIDESTINED.
DID WE PASS?
YOU DID.
IT ACTUALLY MAKES SENSE.
IF DEVIMON HAD DEFEATED YOU,
YOU WOULD NOT BE READY
FOR THIS BIGGER CHALLENGE.
DEVIMON'S POWER WAS NOTHING
COMPARED TO THE DARK MASTER'S.
HE WAS MERELY THE BEGINNING.
BUT YOU'VE PROVEN YOURSELVES
OVER AND OVER
BY DEFEATING ONE EVIL DIGIMON
AFTER ANOTHER.
YOU'RE READY TO TAKE ON
THE DARK MASTERS.
COME ON, WE MUST FIND
YOUR FRIENDS IMMEDIATELY.
WHERE DID THEY GO?
WE CAN'T DO THIS
ALL ALONE.
SOME OF US NEEDED A TIMEOUT
FROM EACH OTHER.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
Leomon: YOU NEEDED
A TIMEOUT?
YEAH, YOU MIGHT SAY
IT'S ANOTHER KIND OF TEST.
ELECTROSHOCKER!
All: AAH!
METEOR WING!
AAH!
[ YELPS ]
HAND OF FATE!
AAH!
LIGHTNING PAW!
Puppetmon: YOU GUYS
ARE ABOUT AS USEFUL
AS A LOAD OF STINKY
ROTTEN VEGETABLES.
I'VE HAD IT WITH YOU.
HUH?
TRY TO STOP US NOW.
AGUMON WARP DIGIVOLVE TO...
WARGREYMON!
TERRAFORCE!
PUPPET PUMMEL.
THINK YOU'RE SO SMART?
NOBODY TOYS WITH ME.
HE'S GOT ME STRUNG UP.
THE ENEMY'S THAT WAY.
WARGREYMON.
DON'T COME TOO CLOSE. I DON'T
KNOW WHAT HE'LL MAKE ME DO.
HUH?
KARI!
GATOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
ANGEWOMON!
GOTCHA!
KEEP RUNNING, KIDS.
I DON'T WANT TO CATCH YOU.
KABUTERIMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
MEGAKABUTERIMON!
BIRDRAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
GARUDAMON!
HORNBUSTER!
AAH!
I-I'M NOT AFRAID OF YOU.
UH, I'LL GET YOU!
IF I WERE YOU,
I'D RECONSIDER.
HUH?
Tree:
WAIT. WE MUST BE CAREFUL.
THE DIGIDESTINED ARE STRONG,
STRONGER THAN I SUSPECTED.
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE THEM
OR IT COULD BE DISASTROUS.
WHAT? SPIT IT OUT ALREADY.
ARE YOU SAYING
I MIGHT LOSE?
I'M ONLY SAYING
TAKE THEM SERIOUSLY.
THE DIGIDESTINED
HAVE SOMETHING YOU DON'T.
HMM? WHAT DOES
HE MEAN BY THAT?
I GOT MORE POWERS
THAN THEY EVER WILL.
FOOLS, I'M NEVER GOING TO LOSE
TO YOU. WATCH!
♪ I KNOW SOMETHING YOU DON'T ♪
GRRAAH!
All: AAH!
[ GROWLING ]
AAH!
Metaletamon:
IT'S SHOWTIME, BABY.
HA HA.
HMM?
IT'S METALETAMON.
HE NEVER QUITS.
ARE YOU TRYING
TO PULL A NUMBER ON ME, BRO?
WELL, I'M GOING TO LAY IT
ON THE LINE
'CAUSE I'M SO FINE.
DEAL WITH ME. THEN WE
SHALL SEE WHO'S FINE.
LEOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
SABERLEOMON!
WHOA! WELL, I SEE
WE BEEN TAKING OUR VITAMINS,
BUT IT'S TIME TO PUT THE CAT
OUT WITH THE GARBAGE.
Tai: SABERLEOMON MAY HAVE
A HEART OF GOLD,
BUT HE'LL CRUSH OPPONENTS
WITH HIS CLAWS OF STEEL.
DON'T DO IT.
I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
NOW RUN BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
HOWLING CRUSHER!
BANANA SLIP!
[ GROWLS ]
OH! AAH!
I'M NOT GOING TO SIT HERE
AND WATCH THIS. WAIT FOR ME!
GOMAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
IKKAKUMON!
MIMI, PLEASE LET ME
FIGHT WITH THEM. WELL?
THEY NEED ME.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
MIMI?
HARPOON TORPEDO!
WAIT!
WE'VE GOT TO HELP HIM OUT.
DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S BETTER TO LEAVE,
LIKE HE TOLD US TO?
BUT, JOE!
TWIN FANG!
HA HA HA!
WHAT?
I THINK WE'D BETTER LEAVE.
WHAT ABOUT LEOMON?
HA HA HA HA! YOU CALL THAT
YOUR BEST SHOT?
METAL PUNCH!
HE'S NOTHING.
IF YOU WANT A REAL
CHALLENGE, IT'S RIGHT HERE.
WHAT?
OGREMON,
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
YOU'RE NO MATCH FOR HIM.
I COULD TAKE ON
THIS TIN CAN IF I WANT TO.
NO!
MIMI!
YOU'RE IN NO SHAPE
TO FIGHT.
STOP IT, AND QUIT TRYING
TO BE A HERO.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
LITTLE DARLING,
TODAY I'M OFFERING
A GROUP DISCOUNT.
BESIDES, IT SAVES ME TIME
TO DESTROY ALL YOU AT ONCE.
AAH!
MIMI, NO!
HA HA HA HA!
OKAY, THAT DOES IT!
IKKAKUMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
ZUDOMON!
LEOMON, WAKE UP! PLEASE
TELL ME YOU'RE ALL RIGHT!
VULCAN'S HAMMER!
AS YOU CAN SEE,
THAT DIDN'T EVEN FAZE ME.
MY METAL'S CHROMIDIGIZOID,
THE ABSOLUTE STRONGEST
METAL THERE IS.
THEN MAYBE YOU'D LIKE THIS.
VULCAN'S HAMMER!
NO MATTER WHAT YOU ATTEMPT,
IT'S USELESS,
'CAUSE I'M INVINCIBLE!
AAH!
I'M BREAKING APART!
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
I LOST MY LUSTER.
WHY DOES THIS
KEEP HAPPENING?
MY HAMMER IS MADE
OF CHROMIDIGIZOID.
IT ISN'T YOUR MOMENT
TO SHINE.
THAT CAN'T BE!
TWIN FANG!
AHH!
YOU'LL PAY BIG TI--
HE DID IT!
LEOMON!
GRRAAH!
DON'T WORRY.
I'VE GOT IT COVERED.
GET MOVING!
AAH!
KARI, COME ON!
WING BLADE!
IT FIZZLED OUT!
MEGAKABUTERIMON!
T.K., HURRY! RUN!
OKAY! GOOD LUCK!
GRRAAH!
HA HA! I'M OUT OF HERE!
HAPPY HOUSEWARMING!
TAKE ME, TOO!
ARE YOU JOKING? DO I LOOK
LIKE I WANT YOUR COMPANY?
TAKE THIS!
PUPPET PUMMEL!
AAH!
WHO'S THAT BEHIND ME?
WELL, IT'S ABOUT TIME!
GET THEM, DO MAJOR DAMAGE,
AND I WANT NO FOUL-UPS!
GRRAAH!
HUH?
WHAT'S WITH YOU?
DAYDREAMING AGAIN, HUH?
NOW, METAL GARURUMON,
SOCK IT TO THEM!
HEY, THIS ISN'T WORKING!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO OBEY ME!
I'M THE BOSS!
THINK AGAIN.
YOU'RE WASHED UP,
PUPPETMON.
NOBODY'S GOING TO BE
ON YOUR SIDE
BECAUSE YOU DON'T CARE
ABOUT THEM.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT THEY THINK.
THEY'RE STILL GOING TO DO
WHAT I TELL THEM TO DO!
AAH!
METAL WOLF CLAW!
JERIMON, WHAT IS IT
THAT THOSE KIDS HAVE
THAT I DON'T?
FRIENDS.
THANK YOU, MATT.
HUH?
HA HA HA.
NOW THAT PUPPETMON'S
BEEN DEFEATED,
THE FOREST
IS DISAPPEARING!
RUN! WE'VE GOT TO GET OUT
AND FIND A SAFE PLACE!
[ ALL GASPING ]
LEOMON, IT'S ME!
COME ON!
YEAH, WAKE UP.
THIS STUPID TOILET PAPER
ISN'T GOING TO BE ANY GOOD.
AAH!
THE FOREST.
THE FOREST IS DISAPPEARING.
[ GASPS ]
IT'S A SIGN THAT SOMETHING
POSITIVE HAS HAPPENED.
YOUR FRIENDS MUST HAVE
DEFEATED PUPPETMON.
THAT'S GOOD.
I EXPECTED THAT THEY WOULD.
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE US.
WE DEPEND ON YOU.
YOU HAVE NO REASON
TO WORRY.
I MUST GO NOW
AND REJUVENATE MYSELF
AT THE PRIMARY VILLAGE.
BUT -- BUT --
OGREMON, I'M VERY SORRY.
NOW IS NOT THE TIME
FOR US TO RESOLVE THINGS,
BUT I PROMISE
WE WILL MEET UP AGAIN.
YOU'RE A GOOD RIVAL.
[ ALL SOBBING ]
[ SOBBING ]
MIMI, LET'S GO
TO THE PRIMARY VILLAGE.
YES, WE NEED HELP,
AND IF WHAT LEOMON SAID
IS TRUE,
WE'LL MEET
SOME OLD FRIENDS THERE.
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT TO SEE
CHUMON AND PIXIMON AGAIN?
WELL, THEN
THE MATTER'S SETTLED.
WE'RE MAKING A TRIP
TO FIND THE PRIMARY VILLAGE,
ALL RIGHT?
THERE'S ONLY ONE PROBLEM.
IT DOESN'T EXIST.
IT'S A GHOST TOWN.
IT WAS DESTROYED
AFTER THE DARK MASTERS
POISONED IT WITH THEIR EVIL.
NO ONE IS LEFT.
IT CAN'T BE.
IT WILL NEVER RETURN
TO THE WAY IT WAS
UNTIL THE DARK MASTERS
ARE ELIMINATED.
ANY IDEAS?
I SAY WE THROW THEM OUT
AND THEN SAVE THE VILLAGE.
THAT WOULD BE GREAT,
AND IT'S BETTER
THAN SITTING AROUND
AND DOING NOTHING.
MIMI, THE ONLY WAY
OUT OF THIS MESS
IS TO DEFEAT
THE DARK MASTERS.
ARE YOU UP FOR IT?
WE NEED YOUR HELP, MIMI.
PLEASE SAY YES.
FOR LEOMON AND EVERYONE --
THE WHOLE DIGIWORLD
NEEDS US.
YES, YOU'RE RIGHT,
PALMON.
SNIVELING IS FOR BABIES,
AND I'VE DONE TOO MUCH
OF THAT ALREADY.
OGREMON, ARE YOU GOING TO
COME ALONG WITH US, HMM?
HUH? WELL, I HAVE
NO INTENTION
OF JOINING FORCES
WITH YOU CRAZY KIDS.
HOWEVER, IF WE ALL HAPPEN
TO BE GOING THE SAME WAY,
I'M STUCK TAGGING ALONG.
DON'T WORRY, OGREMON.
WE WON'T BLOW YOUR COVER.
NOW THAT IT'S DECIDED,
WE NEED TO SEEK OUT
A FEW ALLIES.
THERE MUST BE OTHERS
WHO ARE WILLING TO FIGHT
THE DARK MASTERS.
I KNOW THEY'RE OUT THERE.
WE JUST HAVE TO FIND THEM.
YEAH!
PRINCESS, HOW ABOUT IF WE
COME ALONG TO HELP OUT?
NO WAY.
COME ON!
ONLY IF YOU STOP
CALLING ME PRINCESS
AND CALL ME MIMI
INSTEAD.
OUR PLEASURE, MIMI.
SO CAN WE COME NOW?
OF COURSE YOU CAN.
HA HA HA.
SOME PROBLEMS
ARE CROSSROADS IN LIFE.
IN THE PAST, I AVOIDED IT
BY GOING TO THE MALL,
BUT IT FEELS GOOD
TO DO THE RIGHT THING,
EVEN THOUGH, AT TIMES, THAT
MIGHT BE A DANGEROUS THING.
Man: THE DIGIDESTINED
ARE GATHERING ALLIES,
BUT SEPARATED,
WILL THEY BE ABLE TO SURVIVE
THE COMBINED ATTACK
OF THE DARK MASTERS?
TUNE IN TO THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."