AFTER BEING TRANSPORTED
BACK TO THE DIGIWORLD,
THINGS WERE OBVIOUSLY DIFFERENT
AND MOST DISTURBING.
CHUMON TOLD US OF HOW HE
AND SUKOMON WERE SEPARATED
AND HOW THE DARK MASTERS
NOW RULED THE ENTIRE WORLD
FROM THE NEWLY CREATED
SPIRAL MOUNTAIN.
THESE MEGA DIGIMON
WERE MOST EVIL,
AND PROVED THAT FACT
ON LITTLE CHUMON.
IT SEEMS EIGHT CHAMPION DIGIMON
CAN'T EVEN BEAT ONE MEGA,
SO WE MADE A BREAK FOR IT
WITH THE HELP OF PIXIMON.
HE CREATED A DIVERSION
SO WE COULD GET AWAY.
WHAT A BRAVE LITTLE GUY.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
YOU'RE AS READY
AS YOU'LL EVER BE.
GO GET HIM!
T.K.: I THINK THAT
WAS MEANT TO BE ENCOURAGING.
HE HAS AN AWFUL LOT
OF CONFIDENCE IN US.
YOU MAY HAVE FOOLED
THOSE SILLY CHILDREN
WITH THIS BRAVE ACT,
BUT WE KNOW BETTER,
DON'T WE?
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
IT'S JUST AN ACT?
Mimi: OH, IT DOESN'T SEEM RIGHT
JUST LEAVING HIM THERE.
OH! OH!
Tai: REMEMBER,
HE WANTED IT THIS WAY.
LOOK, THE FOG'S
FINALLY CLEARING.
GREAT. NOW WE CAN CLEARLY SEE
THAT WE'RE LOST.
IT'S MORE PRODUCTIVE
TO THINK OF OURSELVES
AS ON OUR WAY, JOE.
YEAH, I FEEL BETTER ALREADY.
ALL I KNOW IS
I'M GETTING PRETTY HUNGRY.
I'M COLD.
BUT EVERYBODY'S OKAY, RIGHT,
BESIDES BEING HUNGRY
AND COLD AND LOST?
DON'T FORGET FRIGHTENED, TIRED,
AND UPSET ABOUT PIXIMON.
OTHERWISE, WE'RE FINE.
Izzy: I HAVE A FEELING
WE'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE.
WAIT A MINUTE. LOOK!
WHERE?
WHAT?
THOSE SMASHED-UP
PHONE BOOTHS.
Sora: YOU DON'T THINK
THAT THEY COULD BE
THE SAME ONES, DO YOU?
Tai: OF COURSE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THIS WHOLE TIME
WE THOUGHT
WE WERE MAKING
ALL THIS PROGRESS,
BUT NOW IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'VE BEEN TRAVELING
IN ONE BIG CIRCLE.
Piedmon: HOW SMALL
THEY LOOK FROM HERE --
LIKE ANTS.
STRANGE THAT
SUCH LITTLE CREATURES
COULD CAUSE SO MUCH TROUBLE.
THEY WON'T FOR LONG.
THEY'RE STANDING ON THE EDGE
OF MY TERRITORY NOW --
THE SEA. I'LL BE THE ONE
TO FINISH THESE DIGIDESTINED
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
Piedmon: HMM. BOLD WORDS,
BUT YOU'RE NOT THE FIRST
TO MAKE SUCH A BOAST,
METALSEADRAMON.
BUT I WILL BE THE LAST.
THEY'LL BE SHARK BAIT
BEFORE THE DAY IS THROUGH.
HA HA HA.
Matt: SO WE'VE JUST GONE
AROUND IN ONE BIG CIRCLE, HUH?
MAKES THE WHOLE THING SEEM
KIND OF POINTLESS, DOESN'T IT?
HOLD ON. MAYBE THAT'S IT.
MAYBE THE POINTLESSNESS OF IT
IS THE WHOLE POINT.
SAY WHAT?
THANKS FOR THE PHILOSOPHY.
THAT'S A BIG HELP.
Girl: HELP! SAVE ME!
Mimi: LOOK! OUT THERE!
SOMEONE'S DROWNING!
SOMEBODY'S
GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
THEY'RE TOO TIRED.
THEY'LL BE DROWNED THEMSELVES.
OKAY, THEN IN THAT CASE,
WE'LL HAVE TO GO.
NO, WAIT UP, T.K.
KARI.
SOMEONE BIGGER SHOULD GO.
WE CAN USE
THAT OUTRIGGER.
T.K.: I'M COMING.
Kari: ME, TOO.
HEY, WAIT UP.
I'M COMING, TOO.
I CAN HELP.
Girl: HELP ME! HELP!
Matt and Tai: STROKE!
STROKE! STROKE! STROKE!
HA HA HA!
Mimi: DID HIS VOICE
GET LOWER OR WHAT?
[ ROARS ]
TAI, A SEA MONSTER!
YOU COULD SAY THAT AGAIN.
THAT'S SHELLMON, AND HE'S
NOT HERE TO PLAY WATER POLO.
PADDLE LIKE CRAZY!
THERE'S NO ESCAPING.
YOU'RE IN MY ELEMENT NOW.
COME ON. MOVE IT.
Tai: STROKE! STROKE!
STROKE! STROKE!
HA HA HA.
HE'S ON TOP OF US! AAH!
[ ROARS ]
Mimi: OH, THAT BREATH!
EVER HEAR OF FLOSSING?
Tai: STROKE! STROKE!
ARE YOU PADDLING,
OR AM I TALKING TO MYSELF?
Izzy: UH-OH.
[ ROARS ]
WE MAY BE EXHAUSTED,
BUT WE CAN'T JUST SIT HERE.
WE'VE GOT TO HELP.
LEAVE IT TO US.
YOU SAVE YOUR DIGISTRENGTH.
BUKAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GOMAMON!
TANEMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
PALMON!
MOTIMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
TENTOMON!
YOKOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
BIYOMON!
LET'S GO!
POISON IVY!
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
HERE'S MY SPIRAL TWISTER!
SUPER SHOCKER!
COME ON, MARCHING FISHES!
Tai: THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
THIS IS THE WAY TO TRAVEL.
UH-OH.
FORGET THIS.
AAH! UHH!
[ MOANS ]
Tai: I KNOW
THEY'RE ALL DEAD TIRED
AND THEY MAY NOT FEEL LIKE IT
AT THE MOMENT,
BUT I THINK TODAY PROVED
THAT OUR DIGIMON ARE GETTING
STRONGER AND STRONGER.
THAT'D BE GREAT, BUT WHAT
MAKES YOU THINK SO?
I REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
WE TOOK ON SHELLMON.
AGUMON HAD TO DIGEVOLVE
INTO GREYMON
BEFORE WE COULD
FINALLY BEAT HIM,
AND EVEN THEN IT WAS CLOSE.
[ GROWLS ]
AAH!
NOVA BLAST!
HA!
AAH!
BUT THIS TIME THEY BEAT HIM
EASILY WITHOUT GREYMON.
BUT THEY GANGED UP ON HIM.
IT WAS FOUR AGAINST ONE.
BUT THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO
DIGEVOLVE AS FAR TO DO IT.
I STILL SAY IT MEANS
YOU'RE STRONGER
THAN YOU WERE.
OR MAYBE SHELLMON'S
JUST WEAKER.
HOW COME EVERYONE'S
BEING A DOWNER?
I'M TRYING
TO BE POSITIVE HERE.
BESIDES, I STILL CAN'T
GET OUT OF MY MIND
SOMETHING THAT PIXIMON
SAID TO ME.
BUT YOU SAID IT WAS POSSIBLE
TO SAVE THE PLANET
IF THE EIGHT OF US
WERE ALL TOGETHER.
HOW COME IT'S NOT HAPPENING?
WHAT'S UP, PIXIMON?
BEING TOGETHER'S NOT ENOUGH.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
YOU NEED TO DO TO BEAT HIM.
I THINK HE MEANT
WE HAD TO GET STRONGER,
AND THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENING.
TAI'S RIGHT.
I FEEL STRONGER.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
YOU ARE LOOKING KIND OF BUFF.
DO I LOOK STRONGER
TO YOU, IZZY?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAKE A MUSCLE.
I WAS.
DO I LOOK DIFFERENT?
YEAH, YOU LOOK
BUFFED OUT TO THE MAX.
KARI?
YOU DON'T LOOK
ANY DIFFERENT,
BUT GIVE IT TIME,
GATOMON.
YOU'LL CATCH UP
WITH THE REST.
IF YOU SAY SO.
YOUR COAT'S
LOOKING GLOSSIER.
REALLY? YOU THINK?
[ LAUGHING ]
Matt: DID IT GET BRIGHTER
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
OR IS IT JUST
TAI'S SUNNY DISPOSITION?
MAYBE IT'S LIKE A MIRAGE.
HUH?
WAS THAT SHACK THERE BEFORE?
MAYBE SOMEBODY MOVED IN
WHEN WE WERE GONE.
Mimi: SOMETHING SMELLS
SUSPICIOUSLY LIKE FOOD.
LET'S TAKE IT EASY,
EVERYONE.
REMEMBER,
WE'RE IN THE DIGIWORLD,
WHERE NOT EVERYTHING
IS WHAT IT APPEARS TO BE.
LOOKS MAY BE DECEIVING,
BUT SMELLS,
THAT'S SOMETHING ELSE,
AND I DEFINITELY SMELL
GRILLING HAMBURGERS.
SEE? IT'S A SNACK BAR --
BURGERS, SODAS,
ICE CREAM, PIZZA.
Tai: MIRAGE OR NOT,
I'LL TAKE MY CHANCES.
GANGWAY!
[ ALL YELLING ]
SORRY, MIMI.
OH, THANKS.
WHAT ARE YOU TWO
WAITING FOR?
YEAH. THEY'RE GOING TO EAT
EVERYTHING WITHOUT US.
Sora: WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S A TRAP!
HA HA HA. SNACK TIME.
[ ALL GASP ]
Patamon: IT'S SCORPIOMON,
ONE OF METALSEADRAMON'S
FLUNKIES.
BETWEEN HIS PINCHERS
AND HIS TAIL,
IT'S HARD TO KNOW
WHICH END IS WORSE.
SORRY, BUT THE ONLY MUNCHIES
AROUND HERE ARE YOU.
NOW SAY GOOD NIGHT.
IT'S BEDTIME.
YEAH?
YEAH! SCORPION STORM!
[ SCREAMING ]
Sora: CAN'T BREATHE.
CAN'T...
THOSE SOUNDS NEVER MEAN
ANYTHING GOOD.
LET'S GO!
OH, NO.
SOMETHING TELLS ME
THIS MEANS NO CHILI DOGS.
All: HUH?
SHH!
Mimi: OH, WOW.
WHAT'S HAPPENED TO THEM?
ARE THEY...
COULD THEY BE...
AAH!
SHH!
WELL DONE, SCORPIOMON.
THESE DIGIDESTINED
ARE NOT SO DIFFICULT
TO HANDLE AFTER ALL.
HERE'S YOUR REWARD.
OH, CLAMS!
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU, BOSS!
I JUST LOVE CLAMS.
I JUST CAN'T GET
ENOUGH OF THEM.
OW!
SHH!
WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT IS IT, BOSS?
YOU WANT SOME?
QUIET. I THOUGHT
I HEARD SOMETHING.
I DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING.
HMM. WELL,
NOW TO FINISH THEM OFF.
HA HA HA!
EIGHT LITTLE GNATS
AND THEIR DIGIMON ACCOMPLICES.
HMM? WHAT'S THIS?
THERE'S SUPPOSED
TO BE EIGHT OF THEM.
TWO OF THEM ARE MISSING.
YOU CHUCKLE-HEADED
COCKLESHELL!
[ BURPS ]
STOP EATING AND FIND
THE OTHER TWO NOW!
OH, YOU GOT IT.
RIGHT AWAY. I'M ON IT.
[ ALL SCREAM ]
COME BACK HERE!
I HATE IT
WHEN THEY DO THIS.
HEY, SLOW DOWN!
I GOT YOU NOW.
HA HA HA!
TOO MANY CLAMS
FOR LUNCH.
[ PANTING ]
OH, NO, NOT AGAIN!
COME ON! COME ON!
I'M NOT BUILT FOR THIS.
Gomamon: THIS WAY! THIS WAY!
OH, FORGET IT.
I CAN'T RUN ANYMORE.
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
STAND AND FIGHT.
RIGHT.
Gomamon: HUH?
WE MAY NOT HAVE TO.
Mimi: WHAT HAPPENED?
Joe: I DON'T KNOW,
BUT HE'S GONE.
HA HA!
WHAT A LUCKY BREAK.
Mimi: LUCKY FOR US
HE DOESN'T WORK OUT.
OH, I'M GETTING
MY EXERCISE RIGHT NOW.
MY ROOTS ARE EXHAUSTED.
AND I AM SO HUNGRY,
I COULD
JUST ABOUT EAT SEAWEED.
HEY, WAIT! LOOK!
[ LAUGHS ]
HUH?
NOT BAD.
GET YOUR MITTS
OFF MY CLAMS!
[ ALL SCREAM ]
PALMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
TOGEMON!
GOMAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
IKKAKUMON!
SCORPION STORM!
OH, YEAH? HOW ABOUT
SOME NEEDLE SPRAY?
HARPOON TORPEDOES!
IF THE DIGIMON REALLY
ARE GETTING STRONGER,
THEY SHOULD BE ABLE TO HANDLE
SCORPIOMON NO PROBLEM.
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
THEY'RE DOING TOO WELL.
AAH!
OH!
HEY, PUT ME DOWN,
YOU OVERGROWN CRAWDADDY,
BEFORE I GET REALLY ANGRY!
AAH!
WHY DON'T YOU COME OUT
FROM BEHIND YOUR SHELL
AND FIGHT LIKE A CLAM?
I DON'T THINK HE THOUGHT
THAT WAS VERY FUNNY.
SCORPION STORM!
RUN!
HEY, SQUID BREATH,
WE'RE THE ONES YOU WANT.
TAIL BLADE!
OOH, I JUST LOVE CLAMS.
HURRY UP!
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE!
GET MOVING!
DIGEVOLVE, TOGEMON!
TOGEMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
LILLYMON!
IKKAKUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
ZUDOMON!
OKAY, ZUDOMON, LET'S GO!
HUH?
TAIL BLADE!
FLOWER CANNON!
VULCAN'S HAMMER!
GOOD NIGHT.
KARI.
WHERE IS THAT FOOL
WITH THOSE OTHER CHILDREN?
I'M TIRED OF WAITING.
HURRY! FASTER!
WE GOT TO MOVE NOW!
DID YOU REALLY HAVE TO
BRING ALONG A SOUVENIR?
THAT'S DOES IT!
I'LL WORRY ABOUT
THE OTHER TWO CHILDREN LATER.
Mimi: YIKES!
AND I THOUGHT
SHELLMON'S BREATH WAS GNARLY.
HE'LL TOAST THEM
LIKE MARSHMALLOWS.
THIS WAY! HURRY!
HEY, GUYS, NAPTIME'S OVER.
TAI, YOU'VE GOT
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
SORA, GET UP!
MOVE OR YOU'RE GOING
TO BE TOAST!
I MEAN LITERALLY!
EVERYBODY ON YOUR FEET!
HURRY!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ ROARS ]
HANG ON AND KEEP MOVING.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
[ SCREAMING ]
HA! FAREWELL, DIGIDESTINED.
IT WAS A RARE PLEASURE
KNOWING YOU --
MEDIUM RARE.
HA HA HA!
AAH! HOT, HOT, HOT!
HUH?
WHO'S THE HOT-TEMPERED
FOUL-MOUTH WHO --
OH, IT WAS YOU, BOSS.
OKAY. NO PROBLEM.
HUH? NO! NO!
THEY'RE GONE!
ALL OF THEM GONE!
SCORPIOMON,
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
WELL, YOU SEE,
THAT'S A FAIR QUESTION.
SILENCE!
YOU FAILED ME,
AND I WILL NOT
FORGIVE FAILURE!
NO, I DIDN'T THINK THAT --
AAH!
Sora: THEY'RE GONE. WHEW.
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
Tai: BUT WE CAME OUT
OF IT OKAY.
THAT'S WHAT COUNTS.
I HATE TO TELL YOU THIS --
EVERYTHING'S NOT OKAY.
MIMI'S RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
THE DIGIMON STILL
MAY NOT BE STRONG ENOUGH.
BOTH OF OURS
HAD TO DIGEVOLVE AGAIN
BEFORE THEY COULD BEAT
SCORPIOMON,
AND HE WAS A FLUNKY.
FRANKLY, IT'S HARD TO SEE
HOW THEY STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST A FULLY DIGEVOLVED
MONSTER LIKE METALSEADRAMON.
MAYBE PIXIMON
MEANT SOMETHING ELSE
WHEN HE SAID
WE WERE MISSING SOMETHING.
WHATEVER THE SECRET IS,
WE'VE GOT TO FIND IT
IF WE EVER HOPE
TO SAVE THE WORLD.
YES, AND THE SOONER
THE BETTER.
[ ALL SCREAM ]
IT'S METALSEADRAMON AGAIN!
HA HA HA!
I'LL DRY HIM OFF.
ZUDOMON, YOU GET
THE OTHERS OUT OF HERE.
YOO-HOO!
YOU BIG UGLY -- WHOA!
JUST MY LUCK --
HE'S FAST, TOO.
Joe: COME ON, ZUDOMON!
MOVE IT! MOVE IT!
Sora: HAS HE SEEN US?
Tai: I DON'T KNOW,
AND I DON'T WANT TO FIND OUT.
PATHETIC LITTLE FOOLS!
YOU THINK YOU CAN
ESCAPE ME BY SEA?
I THINK IT'S SAFE TO SAY
HE'S SEEN US.
Tentomon: FASTER, ZUDOMON!
WE NEED SPEED!
YEAH. STOP DOG PADDLING.
AHA! TONIGHT YOU SLEEP
WITH THE FISHES.
FLOWER CANNON!
AND AS FOR YOU...
AAH!
LILLYMON!
GOT YOU!
Tai: UH-OH.
Joe: IS HE GONE?
Mimi: I DON'T THINK SO.
Sora: I CAN'T STAND
THIS WAITING.
Matt: I BET
HE'S RIGHT BELOW US.
Tai: SHH! KNOCK IT OFF.
WHOA! HE'S RAMMING US!
HANG ON!
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
AAH!
RIVER OF POWER!
YEOW!
NEVER SEND A ROOKIE
TO DO A MEGA'S WORK.
HA HA HA!
STUCK IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE OCEAN,
THE DIGIDESTINED ARE
AT METALSEADRAMON'S MERCY.
WHAT WILL HAPPEN ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS"?