Matt: I GUESS
IT'S MY TURN TO
FILL YOU GUYS IN.
FIRST, WE HAVE A CLOSE CALL
WITH THESE TWIN METAL
DINOSAUR-LOOKING CREATURES.
THEN, WHEN WE'RE ABOUT
TO CRASH FOR THE NIGHT,
WOULDN'T YOU KNOW IT?
WE'RE CAMPED OUT RIGHT ON TOP
OF A BIG, WICKED SERPENT THING
THAT GOES BY THE NAME
OF SIDRAMON.
THAT'S WHEN THINGS
GOT INTENSE.
I GOT SNATCHED UP
AND GABOMON DIGIVOLVED
INTO A HUGE BLUE WOLF
CALLED GARURUMON.
LUCKY FOR ME,
SIDRAMON WAS NO MATCH.
WHENEVER WE'RE
IN DANGER, OUR DIGIMONS
GET BIGGER AND HELP US.
NOW, THAT'S COOL.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
FOX KIDS WORLDWIDE AND
THE U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGI ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE
THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON! ♪
[WHOOSHING ROAR]
OH, HEY.
WHOA. DID YOU
HEAR THAT?
Matt: IT SEEMS TO BE
SOME SORT OF AIRCRAFT.
Sora: IT LOOKED LIKE
A BIG, FLYING GEAR.
Izzy:
ADMIT IT. MY ALIEN THEORY
IS BECOMING MORE PLAUSIBLE.
Joe: YEAH! THEY HIT US
WITH AN ANTIGRAVITY RAY
TO MAKE US ALL CROOKED!
OR MAYBE THAT SIGN'S
JUST CROOKED.
WHOA!
T.K.!
WHOA. OH...
THAT WAS SCARY!
WATCH IT.
THAT COULD'VE
BEEN A SNAKE
OR WORSE.
OH, BOY. I'M SORRY.
HEY, BIYOMON, ARE THERE
REALLY SNAKES HERE?
NO. JUST GIANT
FLYING KILLER BUGS
AND OTHER UNPLEASANT
DIGIMON.
DON'T YOU WORRY, T.K.,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THEM.
HA HA HA!
OK, NOW
THAT THAT'S SETTLED,
LET'S GET GOING.
NOTHING'S SETTLED,
AND WHERE
WOULD WE GO?
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE WE ARE.
THIS IS SILLY. I SAY
WE KEEP MOVING AND SEE
IF WE CAN FIND ANY SIGNS
OF INTELLIGENT LIFE HERE.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
IS HE SAYING
THAT DIGIMON
ARE NOT INTELLIGENT?
IS THAT WHAT HE'S SAYING?
NOT AT ALL. BUT I THINK
TAI IS RIGHT.
WE NEED TO KEEP MOVING
IN HOPES OF FINDING OUT
WHERE WE ARE.
WE NEED TO STAY CALM
AND STICK TOGETHER.
HUH? LET'S REMEMBER
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER.
TOGETHER SOUNDS GOOD.
WE CAN DO IT.
THIS'LL TAKE TEAMWORK,
AND I'M SURE WE'LL FIGURE OUT
EXACTLY WHERE WE ARE
AND HOW TO GET BACK.
THERE'S NO POINT IN
SPLITTING UP BECAUSE THEN,
ONCE SOMEBODY
DID FIGURE IT OUT--
HEY, SORA!
OPEN YOUR EYES.
WELL, THANKS A LOT
FOR WAITING.
Matt: MOVING
RIGHT ALONG, FOLKS.
KEEP IT MOVING.
OUR NEXT STOP ON THE TOUR
WILL BE THE FOREST
OF IRRELEVANT ROAD SIGNS.
NO PICTURES, PLEASE.
[THINKING] WE'RE LOST,
AND THESE GUYS
ARE MAKING JOKES.
Joe: HEY, WAIT UP.
MY SHOELACE IS BROKEN.
Mimi: YOU NEED NEW SHOES.
WHOO...NEW SHOES.
Matt:
LOOK! TELEPHONE POLES!
I SAY WE FOLLOW THEM
AND SEE WHERE THEY LEAD.
THEY'LL JUST LEAD
TO TROUBLE.
LOOK! IT'S
THE ALIEN SAUCER
AGAIN!
AND IT'S HEADED
FOR A CLOSE ENCOUNTER.
T.K.: BOY, IT'S SO HOT
I CAN FEEL THE HEAT
COMING UP THROUGH MY SOCKS.
Matt: WELL, T.K.,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD PUT
YOUR SHOES BACK ON.
Mimi: OH! THIS
HOT DESERT AIR
IS DESTROYING
MY COMPLEXION.
HOW MUCH FURTHER
IS IT?
Izzy: IS THAT ALL
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT,
MIMI?
WE'LL BE LUCKY IF WE
EVEN SURVIVE THIS HIKE.
Sora: HEY, DOES ANYBODY
BESIDES ME SEE
THAT THESE TELEPHONE POLES
HAVE NO CONNECTING WIRES?
SHE'S RIGHT. I WONDER
IF THESE ACTUALLY ARE
TELEPHONE POLES.
MAYBE THEY'RE SOME
ODD ALIEN EQUIVALENT.
HEY...REMEMBER
THOSE PHONE BOOTHS
AND THAT STREETCAR?
YEAH. WHAT ABOUT THEM?
OH, NOTHING.
I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF ANYBODY ELSE
REMEMBERED.
THAT'S IT! DOOMED!
THE HEAT HAS BAKED
OUR BRAINS.
WE'RE ALL GONNA END UP
LIKE ROASTED PIGLETS.
JUST REMAIN CALM, JOE.
WE'VE ONLY BEEN WALKING
FOR 2 MINUTES.
PSST, IZZY.
COME HERE, IZZY.
I THINK WE BETTER FIND
SOME SHADE FOR JOE
AND QUICK.
[HUMMING]
YOU WON'T BELIEVE
WHAT HAPPENED
TO MY FAVORITE WATCH.
HMM? WHAT?
THE SUN MELTED
THE NUMBERS RIGHT OFF.
MIMI, FOR SOMEBODY
WHO HATES HIKING,
YOU SURE HAVE
A LOT OF COMPASSES.
WHA...
HUH?
OF COURSE, NONE
OF THEM ACTUALLY WORK.
WHOA. THIS DIRT
CONTAINS SMALL
TRACES OF METAL
WHICH COULD AFFECT
THE COMPASS NEEDLE.
Mimi: OH, WELL, I'M
ALWAYS LATE ANYWAY.
THIS IS ONE WEIRD WORLD,
AND I DON'T LIKE IT
ONE LITTLE BIT.
I THINK WE
SHOULD START LOOKING
FOR WATER, GUYS.
OTHERWISE,
WE COULD DEHYDRATE
IN ALL THIS HEAT.
YEAH.
BUT WE'RE DOING OK
FOR NOW, AREN'T WE?
HE-E-E-ELP!
SOMEBODY, PLEASE FIND US!
HELP! OHH!
Izzy: I'VE TAKEN
A SOIL SAMPLE,
MEASURED
THE BAROMETRIC PRESSURE,
AND ANALYZED
THE RELATIVE HUMIDITY.
Sora: AND WHAT
DID YOU FIND OUT?
IT'S REALLY,
REALLY HOT.
Tai: HANG ON JUST
A LITTLE LONGER.
DON'T GIVE UP NOW.
UH...UH...
WE'RE GONNA BE OK.
JUST KEEP MOVING ALONG.
MY HEAD IS BAKING.
IF THIS GOES ON
TOO MUCH LONGER,
I'M GOING TO LOOK
LIKE A WILTED SALAD.
HERE, YOU WEAR
MY HAT FOR A WHILE.
YOU NEED IT
MORE THAN I DO.
THANK YOU, MIMI.
T.K.: PEE-EW!
WHAT'S THAT YUCKY SMELL?
Matt sniffing: OH,
HERE'S A THOUGHT.
NOW YOU KNOW
WHY THEY CALL THEM
SWEAT SOCKS.
THIS BEACH WOULD BE
A LOT MORE POPULAR
IF IT JUST HAD
A COUPLE MORE THINGS
LIKE AN OCEAN,
A GENTLE BREEZE,
SNACK BAR, HUNKY
LIFEGUARDS. TEE-HEE!
HOLD IT.
I HAVE TO STOP.
I JUST
DON'T THINK
I CAN GO
ANY FASTER. HUH.
YOU HAVE TO
STAY POSITIVE.
LET'S ALL PRETEND
THAT IT'S RAINING.
YEAH, HA HA!
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
I SIMPLY ADORE THE RAIN.
ME, TOO, BUT
IT'S TIME FOR
A REALITY CHECK.
THIS
ISN'T GETTING
ANY BETTER.
IT MIGHT BE
A GOOD IDEA
TO TURN AROUND
AND GET OUT
OF THIS DESERT
RIGHT NOW.
YOU MEAN BEFORE WE ALL
HAVE A POWER OUTAGE?
MM-HMM.
I'LL VOTE FOR THAT.
WAIT.
HOLD ON FOR
JUST A SECOND,
EVERYBODY.
IF I'M SEEING
WHAT I THINK
I'M SEEING...
WHAT IS IT, TAI?
IT'S NOT A MIRAGE.
IT'S REAL WATER!
WATER?
THIS IS FANTASTIC!
NOW ALL WE NEED ARE
SOME LEMONS, SUGAR,
AND SOME BIG,
FAT ICE CUBES!
THAT LOOKS LIKE A VILLAGE.
MAYBE WE'LL FIND PEOPLE.
AND SHADE!
MAYBE THEY'LL HAVE
HATS FOR SALE.
HANG ON.
WATER AND FOOD!
I'M
HUNGRY ENOUGH
TO EAT BROCCOLI!
WHAT'S
BROCCOLI? IS
THAT A JOKE?
GREAT! LET'S GET OUT
OF THIS DESERT!
AT LAST!
ALL RIGHT!
YAY!
AAH!
AAH...
HA HA HA!
HEY!
YAY!
HUHHH?
FROM SO FAR AWAY,
EVERYTHING LOOKED SO BIG.
BUT THEY'RE SO CUTE
AND TINY.
OK, QUESTION:
WHO HERE KNOWS
WHERE WE CAN GET
A DRINK?
AND JUST WHAT
DO GIANT DIGIMON DRINK?
ME? I'M NO DIGIMON.
MY FRIEND SORA
IS WHAT'S CALLED
A HUMAN BEING.
YES, WE KNOW
THEY LOOK FUNNY.
IN SPITE OF THIS,
THEY'RE ALL
ACTUALLY VERY NICE.
Together:
WHAT'S A HUMAN BEING?
IF YOU ARE NOT DIGIMON,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE IN DIGIWORLD?
[YOKOMON CLAMORING]
THIS IS GREAT!
THERE IS NO WAY
WE'RE ALL GONNA FIT
INTO THIS PLACE.
RELAX, JOE.
AT LEAST THE NATIVES
HERE ARE FRIENDLY.
OH, MY, I WOULD JUST
LOVE TO TAKE ONE HOME
AND PUT IT ON MY BED
WITH ALL MY OTHER
STUFFED ANIMALS.
Matt: HMPF!
THERE SHE GOES AGAIN.
DO YOU THINK MIMI HEARS
THE SAME THINGS WE HEAR?
I'M NOT SURE ANYMORE.
MAYBE SHE'S AN ALIEN SPY.
T.K. IS TIRED
AND HUNGRY.
HE'S NOT
THE ONLY ONE.
BIYOMON, JUST WHEN
DID YOU DIGIVOLVE?
WHEN I MET SORA.
WE SHARE A SPECIAL BOND,
WHICH IS MAGICAL.
YOU DON'T TALK
LIKE US ANYMORE.
IS THAT HOW
ALL BIYOMON TALK?
NO. IT'S HOW
THE BIG ONES TALK.
I SUPPOSE I JUST
PICKED IT UP FROM SORA.
SHE IS A WONDERFUL
AND KIND HUMAN BEING,
AND I'VE ALREADY
LEARNED A LOT FROM HER.
WE STILL
DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU DIGIVOLVED.
WHAT IS IT
ABOUT BEING AROUND
HUMAN BEINGS
THAT MAKES IT
HAPPEN?
SORA NEEDED ME.
I HAD TO PROTECT HER.
WHEN SHE WAS IN DANGER...
SHE HAD TO PROTECT ME?
A POWER CAME FLOWING
THROUGH ME.
WAIT A SECOND.
NOW I GET IT.
THAT'S WHY SHE'S
ALWAYS FOLLOWING ME
AROUND.
ALL OF A SUDDEN I
REALIZED I'D DIGIVOLVED.
WHEN TAI NEEDED HIM,
AGUMON DIGIVOLVED
TO KOROMON TO PROTECT HIM,
AND GARURUMON
DID THE SAME FOR MATT.
THEY DIGIVOLVED FOR US.
WE'RE LUCKY KIDS.
SORA, WE'RE INVITED
TO HAVE DINNER WITH
THE YOKOS. THEY SAID
THEY'D BE WILLING
TO SHARE THEIR FOOD
WITH ALL OF US.
OH, WOW.
YAY!
LET'S SEE HANDS
IF YOU WANT
LEMONADE.
I WONDER
WHAT YOKOMON EAT.
I'LL TAKE A CHEESEBURGER,
FRIES, AND A SHAKE.
[THINKING] I WONDER
WHAT THEY WILL BE SERVING?
PERHAPS A BONE WITH MEAT...
LETTUCE TOPPED
WITH FISH, OR...
WATER!
WATER?
LOOK, EVERYBODY,
A FRESH-WATER FOUNTAIN!
HURRAY!
ALL THE WATER HERE
IS PIPED IN
FROM A SPRING
AT MIHARASHI
MOUNTAIN.
IT'S THE BEST WATER
IN THE WORLD.
FORGET THE WORLD.
MOUNT MIHARASHI WATER
IS THE BEST
IN ALL THE GALAXY.
WHERE'S
MOUNT MIHARASHI?
Together: OUT THERE!
HEY, THAT'S
A LIVE VOLCANO.
Yoko: YES, BUT THE HEAT
BOILS AWAY ALL THE GERMS.
[GROWLING]
IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN,
THAT NOISE PRECEDES
AN ERUPTION--
AAH!
T.K.: THAT'S COOL, BUT
I STILL DIDN'T GET A DRINK.
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
THE WATER
EVAPORATED.
THAT'S OK, BECAUSE
THE LAKE IS ALWAYS
FULL OF WATER.
I'LL CHECK IT OUT.
LET'S ALL GO.
THE WATER'S ALL GONE.
ALL GONE!
Mimi: GOODNESS!
WHERE DID IT GO?
T.K.: SOMEBODY
PULLED THE PLUG.
Tai: ALL RIGHT,
LET'S NOT PANIC.
[DRY ECHO]
WHAT?
DRY AS A BONE.
I WON'T GIVE UP.
HUH?
[BOOM]
LOOK, TAI'S DOING
A LITTLE DANCE FOR US.
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO STOP
THE FIRE OR BRING DOWN
THE RAIN?
HEY, DO YOU REMEMBER
THAT FLYING GEAR
WE SAW EARLIER?
IT CRASHED RIGHT
INTO A HILLSIDE.
GREAT, OF ALL
THE HILLSIDES OUT THERE,
THE GEAR CRASHES INTO
MIHARISHI MOUNTAIN.
THAT'S THE PLACE
WHERE THE WATER COMES FROM.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE WATER COMES FROM A LAKE
ON THE TOP
OF MOUNT MIHARISHI,
SO A GEAR CRASHING INTO
THE MOUNTAIN COULD AFFECT
OUR WATER SUPPLY.
MM-HMM.
Yoko 2: WE DON'T
DARE GO UP THERE.
THE MOUNTAIN IS GUARDED
BY A FIERY DIGIMON
CALLED MERAMON.
HE'S HIDEOUSLY
DANGEROUS.
I WANT A CLOSER LOOK
AT THAT MOUNTAIN.
YOU SAY THIS CHARACTER
MERAMON IS A FIERY DIGIMON?
WHAT DOES HE LOOK LIKE?
NEVER MIND.
THERE HE IS!
HE'S COMING.
HE'S COMING OUR WAY!
Yoko: HE BURNS UP
EVERYTHING HE TOUCHES!
HE NEVER COMES DOWN
OFF THE MOUNTAIN, THOUGH.
THIS IS VERY STRANGE
BEHAVIOR FOR HIM.
AAH! I'M BURNING!
TOO HOT!
Sora: MERAMON IS
A FIERY DIGIMON.
THERE'S NO REASON
HE SHOULD BE IN PAIN
FROM HIS OWN FLAMES.
THAT'S HIS NATURE.
[CRYING IN PAIN]
THIS IS WEIRD.
HE'S CRYING.
BURNING!
SOUNDS LIKE HE'S
OUT OF HIS MIND WITH PAIN.
WHAT DO WE DO?
BURNING, BURNING, BURNING!
BURNING!
LOOK, HE'S COMING
STRAIGHT TOWARD THE VILLAGE.
Yoko: HEY, EVERYBODY,
WE'D BETTER DECIDE
WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO!
I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM
MOVE SO FAST.
HE'S ALREADY REACHED
THE FOOT OF THE MOUNTAIN
AND NOW HE'S STARTING
TO ENTER THE FOREST.
AAH!AAH!
Sora:
EVERYBODY FREEZE!
STAY VERY STILL.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED MORE
THAN SUNSCREEN TO STOP ME!
HA HA HA!
DON'T MOVE A MUSCLE.
[GROWLING]
BURN! BURN! BURN!
AAH!
UNFREEZE!
[AGONIZING GROWLING]
AND RUN!
AAH!AAH!
UHH!UHH!
UH-HUH.
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
[MENACING LAUGH]
[BREATHING HARD]
AAH!AAH!
[GROWLING]
HA HA HA HA HA!
AAH!AAH!
COME ON,
KEEP IT MOVING!
ALL THE WAY
TO THE REAR.
Matt: OK, SETTLE DOWN,
THERE'S ROOM FOR ALL OF YOU.
WILL YOU PLEASE
STOP SQUIRMING?
HERE'S
THE NEXT BATCH, MATT.
EASY NOW.
YOU'LL BE OK.
WHO'S NOT HERE?
AH!
HA HA HA HA.
THE YOKOS...
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THEM.
THIS IS BAD.
AAH!AAH!
RUN! COME ON!
EVERYONE KEEP MOVING NOW.
JUST FOLLOW THE ONE
IN FRONT OF YOU.
Sora: BIYOMON,
SAVE YOURSELF!
COME DOWN WHILE
THERE'S STILL TIME!
I CAN'T LEAVE HERE UNTIL
ALL MY FRIENDS ARE SAFE, SORA.
ALL RIGHT. I SUPPOSE
I'LL JUST HAVE TO COME
UP THERE AFTER YOU THEN.
HURRY!
SORA,
YOU'LL NEVER MAKE IT!
Joe: HEY,
WHERE'S SORA GOIN'?
Matt: SORA, COME BACK!
AH, GOOD.
THEY'RE ALL SAFE NOW.
Sora:
WATCH OUT!
BIYOMON, HE'S
RIGHT BEHIND YA!
[GROWLING]
GO AWAY, MERAMON,
LEAVE US ALONE!
WE'RE NOT BOTHERING YOU.
AAH!
BIYO! BIYO!
I'M COMING, BIYO!
WHOA!
OHH.
UNH.
ARE YOU OK?
SURE.
I HOPE I NEVER
DO THAT AGAIN.
IT WASN'T VERY FUN.
[LAUGHS]
THANK YOU FOR
COMING TO RESCUE ME.
DON'T MENTION IT.
THAT'S WHAT
A FRIEND IS FOR.
YOU CAN SAY THAT
AGAIN. MY FRIEND.
GRR!
UH-OH!
WE'RE STILL
IN GREAT DANGER, SORA.
WHAT?
YOU STAY HERE.
IT'S MY TURN TO
RESCUE YOU NOW.
YOU THINK YOU'RE
REALLY HOT STUFF.
WELL, YOU'RE IN
BIG TROUBLE NOW.
SPIRAL TWISTER, HA!
UHH!
AAH!
OK, BIG RED, TAKE THAT!
AND THAT!
UHH!
IS THAT THE BEST
YOU HAVE TO OFFER,
WEAKLING?
WE GOT TO HELP HER OUT.
HE'S TOO BIG TO HANDLE!
YEAH!
FIREBALL!
AAH!
HERE, CATCH!
HA HA HA!
OH, NO!
SHE'S HIT!
BIYOMON. OHH.
COME ON, EVERYONE,
WE CAN BEAT THAT MONSTER.
WHAT WE NEED
IS TEAMWORK.
I'M READY.
GIMME YOUR BEST SHOT!
PAH!
YIE!
WAH!
AAH!
Joe: WE NEED
A FIRE EXTINGUISHER.
THAT MADE HIM BIGGER.
YEAH.
[ROARING IN AGONY]
WHY DO I SUFFER SO?
IF WE KNEW WHY
HE WAS CRYING,
IT MIGHT HELP
TO STOP HIM.
FIRE'S NOT
AFFECTING HIM.
I'M GUESSING
IT'S NOT HEARTBURN.
[GROANING]
MAYBE THIS MONSTER JUST
HAS GROWING PAINS.
GROWING PAINS?
MATT, THIS IS
NOT A TIME TO JOKE.
BETTER GET READY.
HERE I COME!
[MENACING LAUGH]
OHH...
SORA?
AAH!AAH!
WE'RE ALL
IN TROUBLE NOW.
MERAMON CANNOT
BE ALLOWED TO WIN.
MY FRIENDS NEED
MY HELP NOW.
WHAT?
[CROWS]
BIYOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
BIRDRAMON!
OHH.OHH.
NO!
[CROWING]
AAH!
WE'LL BE SAFE NOW.
BIYOMON DIGIVOLVED
TO RESCUE US.
[CROWING]
[GRUNTS]
WHAT'S WRONG,
BIRDRAMON AFRAID OF ME?
LET'S FIGHT!
HA HA HA HA!
HERE, HAVE A BALL!
UHH!
DON'T TURN YOUR BACK!
[CROWING]
[MENACING LAUGH]
UHH! UNH! UHH! UNH!
BIRDRAMON, MOVE AWAY!
[SHRIEKS]
GRR--HUH?
AAH!
OHH.
IT WAS A GEAR.
WHAT IS IT?
IT MADE HIM CRAZY.
RIGHT!
I SUPPOSE IF YOU HAD
A BIG BLACK GEAR
STUCK INSIDE OF YOU,
YOU'D ACT
A LITTLE CRAZY, TOO.
THE POOR GUY.
YAY, BIYOMON DID IT!
WOW, EVERY TIME
I'M IN DANGER,
BIYOMON COMES
TO MY RESCUE.
THAT'S WHAT
I CALL A FRIEND.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH, SORA!
OH, BI, I WAS
SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE GREAT.
I CAN'T BEGIN TO TELL YOU
HOW PROUD I AM OF YOU.
I WASN'T
THE LEAST BIT AFRAID.
ALL I COULD THINK ABOUT
WAS SAVING YOU.
BECAUSE--
WELL, YOU KNOW.
OHH.
MERAMON, WHY DID YOU
ATTACK OUR VILLAGE?
I COULDN'T
STOP MYSELF.
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN
AWFUL FOR YOU.
IF YOU COULDN'T
CONTROL YOURSELF,
WHO WAS CONTROLLING YOU?
THE LAST THING
I REMEMBER IS BEING
HIT BY THAT GEAR.
WELL, WE'RE JUST HAPPY TO SEE
THAT YOU'RE BACK TO NORMAL.
I HOPE NOTHING LIKE THIS
EVER HAPPENS AGAIN.
YOU'RE NEEDED TO PROTECT
MOUNT MIHARISHI.
GOOD-BYE, MERAMON!
MAY YOU ALWAYS STAY WELL.
GOOD-BYE! AND PLEASE,
TRY NOT TO BURN DOWN
OUR VILLAGE ANYMORE, OK?
HEY, I JUST REMEMBERED
YOU NEVER GOT THAT DINNER
WE PROMISED YOU.
YOU MUST BE STARVING.
MY TUMMY'S READY
FOR SOME ACTION.
YEAH, LET'S GO!
LET'S EAT!
Tai: WHAT IS THIS STUFF?
Mimi: BE POLITE
AND JUST EAT IT.
A GRACIOUS GUEST NEVER
INSULTS HIS HOST'S COOKING.
HMM. I CAN'T TELL
IF IT'S EVEN BEEN COOKED.
NUM-NUM...
EAT AS MUCH
AS YOU WANT.
WE HAVE MORE THAN
ENOUGH FOR SECONDS.
Tai: YEAH, WELL,
THERE'S PROBABLY
A GOOD REASON FOR THAT.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I WAS AFRAID YOU
WERE GOING TO SAY.
IT SMELLS BETTER
THAN BROCCOLI.
AND WHO KNOWS,
IT MIGHT TASTE BETTER.
HAS ANYBODY NOTICED...
WE TALK A LOT ABOUT FOOD?
NAH, I'M NOT HUNGRY.
I'M SKIPPING
THIS ONE, TOO.
I JUST DON'T LIKE TO EAT
ON AN EMPTY STOMACH.
BESIDES, I DON'T EVEN
KNOW WHAT THAT STUFF IS,
BUT I'M SURE
I'M ALLERGIC TO IT.
[LAUGHING]
HA HA HA HA HA.
HA HA HA.
Sora: AND SO ENDS MY BIGGEST
ADVENTURE YET WITH BIYOMON.
ONE THING'S FOR CERTAIN:
FOR BEING SO LITTLE,
SHE SURE HAS A HUGE HEART.