Mimi:
WE WERE UNDERGROUND
WHEN WE MET THE MOST DIGUSTING CREATURES,
THE NUMEMONS.
WE GET OUTSIDE AND THERE'S LIKE
THIS GIANT STUFFED BEAR
NAMED MONZUMON ATTACKING US
WITH HIS FLOATING HEARTS.
ME AND PALMON GOT AWAY
BUT THE REST OF THE KIDS
GOT LIKE HYPNOTISED
AND TAKEN TO TOY TOWN
HERE THE TOYS
PLAY WITH THE CHILDREN.
THINGS WERE TOTALLY LIKE BAD.
THAT'S WHEN THE ICKY NUMEMONS
CAME TO HELP.
PALMON DIGIVOLVED TO TOKAMON
AND SAVED THE DAY.
NOT BAD FOR A PLANT, HUH?
♪ DI-DI-DI,
DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE INTO
DIGITS OF CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON INTO ULTIMATE-- ♪
♪ ( bird cry ) ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Gomamon:
I KNOW THIS IS NO DAY
AT THE BEACH, JOE,
BUT THAT'S NO REASON
TO BE A WORRY WART ABOUT IT
AND MAKE ALL YOUR FRIENDS
UNHAPPY.
PARDON THE PUN, BUT
CHILL OUT.
ONLY YOU HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH THE COLD.
RIGHT, GUYS?
EVERYONE THINK WARM.
Joe:
I'M ALLERGIC TO FUR.
AH, COME ON
YOU GUYS!--
THE COLD ISN'T
THAT TERRIBLE.
All:
Shivering sounds!
NOT IF YOUR A POLAR BEAR
OR PENGUIN.
YEAH, BUT IF IT SNOWS
WE'LL THROW SOME SNOWBALLS.
Mimi:
AND MAKE SNOWMEN.
T.K:
WHAT DO YOU THINK
SNOWON IS?
Patamon:
A DIGIMON FROM THERE PLANET.
IT'S DIFFICULT TO EXPLAIN.
Tentomon:
WELL, IF IT'S EDIBLE,
COUNT ME IN,
THE BEST THING
ABOUT SNOWBALLS
IS THAT YOU CAN
THROW THEM EASY.
IT'S A FUN GAME
TO PLAY IN WINTER.
THROW FOOD?
WE COULD EVEN BUILD
A SNOW FORT.
YOU DON'T NEED ONE.
Sora:
I BET I CAN BEAT YOU BOTH
BLINDFOLDED!
T.K.:
I WANT TO BUILD AN IGLOO.
I'LL HELP, IF YOU TELL ME
WHAT IT IS.
Tentomon:
AN IGLOO SOUNDS SCRUMPTOUS
TO ME.
TOO BAD THEY'RE NOT EDIBLE
COME ON,
GET SERIOUS.
IT WOULD BE HORRIBLE IF STARTED
SNOWING RIGHT NOW.
LIGHTEN UP A LITTLE, JOE.
WE'RE JUST TRYING TO LOOK ON THE
POSITIVE SIDE OF THINGS.
BLAH!
HEY TAI,
WHEN'S IT GOING TO SNOW?
PROBABLY ANY SECOND NOW.
RIGHT ON JOE'S HEAD.
THAT WOULD BE SO FUNNY.
I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE HIS FACE.
IF THE TEMPERATURE DROPS ANY
LOWER THAN IT IS ALREADY
WE WON'T BE ABLE TO CAMP OUT
ANY MORE.
WE'LL BE FROZEN DIGI-TREATS
( All laughing )
Joe:
GO AHEAD AND LAUGH.
WHEN YOUR TOOTSIES FREEZE
I'LL JUST SAY I TOLD YOU SO.
IT IS ALWAYS BETTER TO SAFE
THEN SORRY.
THINK FIRST.
Gomamon:
WHAT'S THAT WHITE STUFF.
Mimi:
IT'S SNOW!
THERE'S BOUND TO BE
A SKI RESORT NEAR BY.
Whimpering:
OH, MAN!
THIS IS MUCH WORSE
THAN EVEN I THOUGHT.
Sora:
WHAT NOW, GUYS?
Tai:
I THINK WE SHOULD
KEEP GOING.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO GET ANYWHERE
JUST SITTING HERE.
( T.K laughing )
Matt:
IF YOU WALK ACROSS THE FIELD
IN OUR SNEAKERS.
OUR TOES WILL GO NUMB.
Joe:
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO CONTINUE.
Tai:
SO WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSE TO DO?
JUST STAND HERE
LIKE A BUNCH DORKS.
WE EITHER GO ACROSS THE FIELD
OR CLIMB UP THAT BIG MOUNTAIN.
WHOA THERE!
WAIT A SEC.
( sniffing )
I THINK THERE'S A WEIRD ODOR
IN THE AIR.
I DO BELIEVE HE'S RIGHT.
WHAT COULD IT BE?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IT SMELLS LIKE...
( sniffing )
VERY FAMILIAR.
Piyomon:
IT'S STEAM.
SHE'S RIGHT!
BUT WHERE'S IT COMING FROM?
A BIG GEYSER!
YEAH!
All:
WOW! A HOT SPRING!
Mimi:
YIPPEE! NOW I CAN TAKE A BATH! T.K.:
AND WE CAN GET WARM!
( all cheering )
( bubbling sounds )
UH-OH...THIS WATER'S
MUCH TOO HOT!
WE'D BE COOKED IF WE
JUMPED IN THIS.
YES, BOILED.
THERE GO MY BIG DREAMS
OF A NICE WARM BATH.
IT LOOKS SO INVITING!
YEAH, IF YOU WERE
A VEGETABLE.
WHAT'S A LITTLE DIRT
COMPARED TO STARVING?
WE NEED TO FIND SOMETHING
TO EAT
AND THERE'S NOTHING IN SIGHT.
T.K.:
OH YES, THERE IS.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THERE'S NOTHING HERE BUT A BUNCH
OF ROCKS AND BOILING WATER.
LOOKIT!
HUH?
TELL ME I'M NOT
IMAGINING THIS.
HUH?
YEAH!
IT'S FOR REAL!
COME ON,
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
Joe:
WHAT WOULD A REFRIGERATOR
BE DOING WAY OUT HERE?
Matt:
WHERE THERE'S A FRIDGE,
THERE'S GRUB!
Joe:
THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
Sora:
WE WON'T KNOW TILL
WE OPEN IT.
Joe:
I DON'T REALLY
THINK THAT'S--
Mimi:
I WANT HOT COCOA!
Tai:
COME ON, ALREADY--
LET'S SEE WHAT'S IN THERE!
WHOA...EGGS!
THERE MUST BE A ZILLION OF 'EM.
GRUB ON! THESE'LL KEEP US FED
FOR A MONTH.
WAIT! YOU SHOULDN'T EVEN
TOUCH THEM!
WE DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE
FIT FOR HUMAN CONSUMPTION!
I'LL BE THE GUINEA PIG.
IF I TURN PURPLE,
YOU'LL KNOW THEY'RE INEDIBLE.
THERE'S MORE TO IT
THAN THAT.
EVEN IF THEY'RE EDIBLE,
THEY DON'T BELONG TO US.
IT'D MAKE US ALL THIEVES.
YOU GOTTA THINK ABOUT
THINGS LIKE THAT.
UNLESS YOU'RE INTO EATING ROCKS,
WE DON'T HAVE TOO MUCH CHOICE.
I'M SURE THEY'D SAY YES
IF THEY KNEW WE WERE IN TROUBLE.
EXACTLY--WE'D TELL 'EM
IT'S AN EMERGENCY.
RATIONALIZE AWAY.
HMM...
Sora:
SUNNY SIDE UP EGGS
ARE MY SPECIALTY!
( sizzling sounds )
Patamon:
THEY'RE DONE!
COME ON, MAN,
HOW ARE THOSE CHOPSTICKS COMING?
Sora:
HURRY! WE WANT TO EAT!
SORRY, THIS JUST MAKE ME
FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
WE'D BE IN TROUBLE
IF SOMEONE GOT SICK--
NO DOCTORS, YOU KNOW.
I'M ALWAYS THE ONE TO
THINK ABOUT THESE THINGS.
Mimi:
TRES GOURMET!
Piymon:
GO ON! DIG IN!
I HAVEN'T HAD A MEAL LIKE THIS
IN A LONG TIME.
MY STOMACH'S CHIMIN'!
Matt:
IF WE HAD SOME KETCHUP,
IT WOULD BE PERFECT!
T.K.:
I LOVE KETCHUP AND EGGS!
Sora:
THAT SOUNDS GROSS!
WHAT'S THAT MATTER,
YOU HAVEN'T EATEN ANYTHING?
HUH?
I WAS JUST THINKING THAT IF WE
COULD GO HOME,
KETCHUP WOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM.
OH WELL.
NOW I'M HOMESICK--
HOW DEPRESSING.
YOU'RE RIGHT--
NOW I WANT TO GO HOME.
IT'S BEEN FOUR DAYS
SINCE WE'VE BEEN HERE,
AND I DON' KNOW IF ANYONE'S
TRIED TO FIND OUT WHERE WE ARE.
CHEER UP!
TELL ME HOW YOU LIKE YOUR EGGS
AND I'LL TRY TO DO
MY VERY BEST.
I PREFER MY EGGS
WITH SALT AND PEPPER,
BUT I GUESS IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I LIKE SOY SAUCE.
HOW ABOUT SALSA?
HOW ABOUT A REALITY CHECK?
I'LL HAVE MY MINE
WITH MUSTARD AND JELLYBEANS.
HA HA HA!
GROSS!
JELLYBEANS--
THAT SOUNDS GOOD!
YOU'RE BOTH WEIRD.
MY FAVORITE IS EGGS
TOPPED WITH MAPLE SYRUP--YUMMY!
SOMETIMES I LIKE THEM
WITH CHERRIES ON TOP!
THAT'S WEIRD.
T.K.:
BUT I BET IT'S GOOD!
( all giggling )
YOU'RE MAKING ME
COMPLETELY LOSE MY APPETITE.
I JUST LIKE PLAIN EGGS!
I WISH WE COULD TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING BESIDES EGG RECIPES.
DON'T BE SO HARD ON YOURSELF--'
WE'RE JUST HAVING FUN.
JOIN THE PARTY!
I THINK IT'S
TOO LATE FOR HIM.
I THINK JOE THINKS
WE'VE GONE EGG-CRAZY.
WELL, REALLY!
JELLYBEANS AND CHERRIES
ON EGGS--THAT'S CRAZY!
SALT AND PEPPER'S
ALL WE NEED.
KEEP IT SIMPLE--
THAT'S MY MOTTO.
I'M AFRAID JOE'S
JUST NOT ADAPTABLE.
JUST WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
FACE IT--YOU'RE
A STICK IN THE MUD,
IF YOU GET MY DRIFT.
Joe:
I'M PRACTICAL!
Gomamon:
YOU'RE STUFFY!
IT NEVER FAILS--
HERE THEY GO AGAIN.
Gomamon:
YOU WANNA FIGHT?
HUH? HUH?
YEAH, SURE!
HEY! CALM DOWN!
I AM CALM--
HE'S THE ON WHO'S DINGY!
WHY'D YOU SQUEEZE MY ARM?
YOU DON'T SEEM
TO BE YOURSELF TODAY, JOE.
YOU'RE A BASKET CASE.
I AM JUST TRYING TO BE CAREFUL--
UNLIKE THE REST OF YOU WEIRDOS.
I'M TELLING YOU--
YOU'RE ALL ASKING FOR TROUBLE.
( bubbling sounds )
( sighs )
I'VE GOTTA BE
THE CAUTIOUS ONE AROUND HERE.
I HAVE TO BE...
THE VOICE OF REASON.
I HAVE TO...
Tai:
WHY ARE YOU MAKING SUCH
A BIG DEAL OUT OF THIS?
Matt:
BECAUSE IT'S
WAY TOO DANGEROUS!
THERE'S NO PLACE ELSE TO GO--
WE HAVE NO CHOICE!
BEFORE WE DO
SOMETHING FOOLISH,
WE SHOULD THINK IT OVER
A LITTLE MORE!
Tai:
YOU'RE JUST CHICKEN!
Joe:
WHAT'S THE RUCKUS ABOUT?
WHY ARE MATT
AND TAI FIGHTING?
Matt: I AM NOT!
Tai: YOU ARE TOO!
THEY'RE DEBATING WHETHER WE
SHOULD CLIMB INFINITY MOUNTAIN
WHICH IS WAY OVER THERE.
THAT'S PRACTICALLY
UP TO THE SKY.
Tentomon:
IT'S A DOOZY,
THAT'S FOR SURE!
IT'S THE PERFECT SPOT!
WE GOTTA CLIMB UP THERE--
IT'S THE BEST VIEW
OF THE ISLAND.
Joe:
YOU'VE GOT TO ADMIT
HE HAS A POINT.
Sora:
THAT'S NOT
HOW MATT SEES IT.
NOBODY WOULD MAKE IT
UP THAT PEAK.
IT'S MUCH TOO
BIG OF A GAMBLE.
HE MIGHT BE RIGHT.
THERE COULD BE LOTS OF
EVIL DIGIMON UP THAT PEAK.
THAT'S NOT GOOD--
IT WOULDNT' BE WORTH THE RISK.
DON'T BE A WIMP!
WE WON'T GET ANYWHERE
IF WE JUST STAND AROUND TALKING.
PUT YOUR FISTS DOWN
WHEN YOU TALK TO ME
AND STOP ACTING LIKE YOU CAN
BULLY YOUR WAY TO BEING LEADER.
WHAT?!
KNOCK IT OFF
AND CHILL OUT!
LET'S BE SENSIBLE.
SO WHAT'S YOUR OPINION
ABOUT THIS, JOE?
HUH?
Tai:
YEAH--TELL US WHO'S RIGHT,
ME OR MATT?
UH, UH..
WELL, I THINK TAI'S RIGHT
ABOUT GOING UP THAT PEAK.
IF WE WENT UP THERE
WE'D BE ABLE TO SEE THE ISLAND'S
LANDSCAPE A LOT BETTER.
SEE, MATT?
HOLD ON--MATT BROUGHT UP
A GOOD POINT ABOUT THE DANGER.
IT'D BE KIND OF DUMB
TO LEAD EVERYONE UP TO A PLACE
WE KNOW NOTHING ABOUT--
IT WOULDN'T BE SAFE.
HMM.
LET'S GO AS FAR AS WE CAN
UP THE MOUNTAIN!
BUT WE CAN'T PROTECT OURSELVES
OUT THERE!
STOP IT--YOU'RE BOTH
MAKING ME A NERVOUS WRECK!
GIVE ME A CHANCE TO THINK.
DON'T BE DIFFICULT.
YOU'RE THE MOST DIFFICULT PERSON
I EVER MET!
I AM TRYING
TO MAKE A DECISION HERE!
YOU'RE JUST CHICKEN, MATT!
TAKE THAT BACK!
ENOUGH! YOU'RE GIVING ME
A HEADACHE!
GROW UP, YOU THREE--
WE HAVE TO DECIDE WHAT TO DO.
IT'S GONNA GET DARK SOON!
THERE WILL BE PLENT OF TIME
TO ARGUE LATER.
WE NEED TO FIND
A GOOD PLACE TO SLEEP.
Sora:
LET'S HEAD FOR THE CAVE.
Piymon:
I WANT THE TOP ROCK!
SOMEONE'S GONNA GET HURT
IF I DON'T DO SOMETHING FAST.
BUT HOW?
I COULDN'T EVEN STOP THE FIGHT.
INSTEAD, I GOT INVOLVED MYSELF.
THAT WASN'T TOO SMART.
IF I'M RESPONSIBLE
FOR EVERYONE'S SAFETY,
THEN I HAVE TO PROTECT THEM--
THEIR LIVES DEPEND ON ME.
I'LL DO IT.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
GOOD AT CLIMBING--
I'VE GOT THE BEST CHANCE
OF MAKING IT TO THE TOP.
Gomamon:
WHOA THERE!
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO, JOE?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA CLIMB
THAT MOUNTAIN BY YOURSELF,
ARE YOU?
GOMAMON?
YEP--FORGOTTEN ME ALREADY?
WHY DON'T YOU
GO GET SOME SLEEP.
NOT HAPPENING.
Joe:
YES IT IS.
I DON'T THINK SO.
Joe:
HMM.
YOU'RE NOT GOING,
SO QUIT FOLLOWING ME AROUND.
I'M NOT--I HAVE SOME BUSINESS
TO TAKE CARE OF UP THERE.
EVERYTHING DOESN'T
REVOLVE AROUND YOU.
FINE THEN.
( whispers: )
SOMETIMES I JUST
HAVE TO TRICK HIM.
DID YOU
JUST SAY SOMETHING?
UH, YEAH,
NICE NIGHT FOR A WALK.
YOU'RE NUTS.
WHAT'S SO BAD ABOUT THAT?--
I SURE HAVE MORE FUN!
HMM...
( Joe panting )
INFINITY MOUNTAIN IS
A LOT BIGGER THAN I THOUGHT.
ARE YOU READY TO QUIT?--
WE CAN TURN AROUND.
OF COURSE NOT--OOH!
I CAN GIVE YOU A HAND.
OH--YOU CALL THAT A HAND?
WATCH IT.
I WAS KIDDING--
LIGHTEN UP.
HUH?
WHAT'S WRONG?
I THINK YOU ACTUALLY
HAVE A SENSE OF HUMOR.
WHAT?
MAYBE NOT--LET'S GO.
Joe:
YIKES!
Gomamon:
I COULD USE A LIFT.
I'M READY TO TAKE A REST.
Joe:
LOOKS TO ME LIKE WE'RE
HALFWAY THERE.
WE MAKE QUITE A TEAM.
ACTUALLY, WE DO.
( rumbling )
EARTHQUAKE?
WHAT'S THAT?
YOU DON'T THINK
THIS MOUNTAIN IS A...
VOLACANO!!
LOOK UP THERE!
Gamamon:
THE BLACK GEAR.
Joe:
THEY'RE COMING FROM
THE TOP OF THE MOUNTAIN.
I GUESS THERE'S NO RUNNING AWAY
THIS TIME--LET'S GO!
HMM.
Joe:
I'M SURE I SAW 'EM HERE--
WHERE COULD THEY HAVE GONE?
Gomamon:
WOULD IT BE TOO MUCH TO HOPE
THEY DISAPPEARED ALTOGETHER?
WE'LL HAVE TO CLIMB UP THERE
AND SEE.
HUH?
THAT SOUND--
WAY UP THERE.
( horse whinnying )
Joe:
OH, THAT'S JUST GREAT--
A FLYING HORSE WEARING A MASK--
THIS CAN'T BE GOOD.
Gomamon:
THAT'S NOT
YOUR EVERYDAY FLYING HORSE, JOE.
THAT'S UNIMON--
HE'S A WISE OLD DIGIMON.
I NEVER KNEW HE LIVED UP HERE--
HE'S NOT MUCH OF A TALKER.
Joe:
HIDE!
Gomamon:
UNIMON'S VERY GENTLE--
WE DON'T HAVE TO HIDE FROM HIM.
Joe:
YOUR INFORMATION
HASN'T ALWAYS BEEN RELIABLE.
Gormanon:
COLD, BUT TRUE.
HE MUST BE COMING DOWN
TO HAVE A DRINK.
Joe:
I GUESS
THAT'S HIS WATERING HOLE.
Gomamon:
I TOLD YOU
HE WAS A NICE DIGIMON--
HE WOULDN'T HURT A FLY.
WOW--WHAT A BEAUTIFUL HORSE.
MAYBE UNIMON WILL TELL US
WHAT WE NEED TO KNOW--
GOMAMON!
HELLO UNIMON--
IT'S ME, GOMAMON.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE WE--
HUH?
Joe:
WHAT IS IT?
I HEAR SOMETHING--
OUT THERE.
( sinister whooshing sounds )
HUH? WHERE?
Gomamon:
SOMETHING'S COMING TOWARDS US--
CAN'T YOU SEE IT?
OH NO!
IT'S THE BLACK GEAR!
(Unimon whinnies in pain )
GOSH, THINK HE'S IN TROUBLE?
WE'LL HAVE TO SEE.
Gomamon:
UH-OH, LOOK AT HIS EYES--
WE'RE THE ONES
WHO ARE IN TROUBLE!
Joe:
FOR ONCE WE AGREE!
Black Gear:
HELLO, GOMAMON,
AREN'T YOU HAPPY TO SEE ME?
I SURE SLEPT WELL.
I WONDER WHERE SLEEPY JOE IS?
JOE! WHERE'D YOU GO?
HE WOULDN'T BE CLIMBING
THAT MOUNTAIN ALONE, WOULD HE?
EVERYBODY WAKE UP!
WE HAVE AN EMERGENCY!
Black Gear:
HAVING A GOOD TIME, DEAR GUESTS?
I'M IN THE MOOD FOR
A GAME OF AERIAL ATTACK!
DO SOMETHING, GOMAMON!
WHAT??
Black Gear:
YOU'RE NOT THINKING OF LEAVING,
ARE YOU?
THAT'S A PERFECTLY SAFE ROAD
IF YOU'RE
THINKING OF FLYING AWAY!
( growling )
WE NEED SOME HELP!
Black Gear:
AERIAL ATTACK!
( whimpering in fear )
Joe:
BIRDRAMON!
WE'VE COME TO SAVE YOU.
JUST IN TIME, I'D SAY.
Sora:
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
AERIAL ATTACK! YEA!!
BIRDRAMON!
AGUAMON DIGIVOLVE INTO...
GREYMON!
ARGH!
GREYMON,
ARE YOU GONNA BE ALL RIGHT?
Greymon:
I'M STYLIN', DUDE!
WHA--?
HMM.
NOVA BLAST...ARRGH!
YEAH!
GREYMON AND TAI
ARE IN BIG TROUBLE!
OH NO!
HE'S GOING AFTER SORA!
Black Gear:
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
ANOTHER UNINVITED GUEST?
METEOR WING!
WHOA!
SORA!
Black Gear:
HA HA HA HA!
THE GEAR!
I'LL GET IT.
THIS IS CRAZY...
AAAHHHH!!!
COME ON, NOW.
HANG ON!
OH NO--IT WON'T BUDGE!
EEEEEE!!
AAH!
JOE, STOP--
DON'T TRY TO BE A HERO!
I KNOW, BUT I JUST
HAVE TO DO THIS ONE THING.
I'M NOT GOING TO STOP
UNTIL IT'S DONE!
AH!
I HAVE TO THINK POSITIVE!
I'M RESPONSIBLE--
I'VE GOTTA DO IT!
OH, NO!
AAAHHHH!
NOOOOOO!
( futuristic sounds )
GOMAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
IKKAKUMON!
AAAHHH!!
Ikkakumon:
HOLD ON TIGHT, JOE,
WE'RE GOING FOR A RIDE!
AERIAL ATTACK!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
YOU MISSED HIM--
HE'S MUCH TOO FAST FOR US!
( shattering sounds )
Joe:
THE BLACK GEAR JUST DISSOLVED!
YEAH! YOU SAVED THE DAY!
Greymon:
I HOPE I DIDN'T
SHAKE YOU TOO MUCH, TAI.
NAAH!
Sora:
THAT WAS A REALLY CLOSE CALL!
GOOD JOB--THAT'S WHAT I CALL
PULLING IT TOGETHER.
Tai:
WOW, JOE,
YOU WERE JAMMIN' OUT THERE.
YOU'RE A PRETTY GOOD DUDE
AFTER ALL.
YOU WERE SO AWESOME
IT MADE IT POSSIBLE
FOR GOMAMON TO DIGIVOLVE!
Gomamon:
THAT'S NOT WHY I DID IT!
IT'S BECAUSE
I'M JUST A NICE GUY
AND BESIDES, JOE WOULD HAVE
FALLEN ON HIS HEAD.
I DIDN'T HAVE
ANYTHING BETTER TO DO, ANYWAY.
IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME,
PUT UP YOUR DUKES
AND LET'S FIGHT ABOUT IT.
JUST CHILL, GOMAMON--
YOU'RE THE BEST,
AND HEROS DON'T HAVE TO FIGHT!
UHM, OH...HEROS?
UH OH!
♪ GOMAMON'S EM-BARRASSED! ♪
NO WAY,
I'M NO SUCH THING!
COME ON, EVERYONE--
WE'RE ALMOST THERE!
LET'S GO ALL THE WAY
UP TO THE TOP!
Tai:
ALL RIGHT!
I KNEW WE COULD DO IT!
( all cheering )
WHOA...
NOT MUCH OUT THERE.
Joe:
SO GOMAMON AND I
FOUGHT ALL THE WAY TO THE TOP
TO SEE WHAT WAS THERE,
AND WE FOUND,
WELL...NOTHING.
BUT I THINK WE DISCOVERED
QUITE A BIT ON THE WAY UP.