Matt:
T.K WAS THE NEXT
TO FIND HIS CREST,
AND IT LED US TO A PLACE
WHERE IZZY MADE
QUITE A DISCOVERY.
HE CAME TO THE CONCLUSION
THAT WE ARE INSIDE
A GIANT PROGRAM,
AND EVEN US KIDS ARE JUST
PIECES OF COMPUTER DATA.
WITH THIS NEW INFORMATION,
TAI THINKS HE IS INVINCIBLE.
THEN WE WERE SENT AN E-MAIL
BY SOMEONE BEING HELD BY ETEMON.
FOLLOWING THE SIGNAL,
WE FOUND DATAMON,
A ROBOT-LIKE DIGI WHO CONTROLS
ETEMON'S NETWORK.
WE RELEASED HIM FROM ETEMON
AND THEN HE TOOK SORA...
NICE GUY, HUH?
♪ DI-DI-DI,
DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE INTO
DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE-- ♪
♪ ( bird cry ) ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Tentamon:
WHEN DATAMON WASN'T ABLE TO GET
HIS REVENGE ON ETEMON,
HE KIDNAPPED SORA AND BIYOMON
AND TOOK OFF.
Joe:
WE DON'T HAVE A CLUE WHERE
TO START LOOKING FOR THEM.
BESIDES, WE CAN ALL
END UP DEAD...OR WORSE!
WHAT IF DATAMON
DOES SOMETHING TO SORA
BEFORE WE CAN RESCUE HER?
LOOK TAI, HE'S ALREADY BEATEN
OUR BRAINS OUT ONCE.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
HE WON'T DO IT AGAIN?
WE NEED TO COME UP WITH A PLAN
BEFORE WE GO ANYWHERE.
THIS MORE DEPRESSING
THAN A SOAP OPERA.
( short sigh )
T.K.:
WE BETTER GET SOME SLEEP.
I'LL STAY HERE JUST IN CASE
YOU GUYS GET SCARED.
YEAH.
THANKS.
T.K.:
GOODNIGHT GUYS.
( light snoring )
Matt:
IT'S TOUGH NOT KNOWIN'
WHAT TO DO.
THE MINUTE I SAW WHAT HAPPENED
I SHOULD HAVE WENT AFTER HER.
IT'S NO USE
BLAMING YOURSELF, TAI...
WE'RE ALL TO BLAME.
YEAH, AND WE'RE ALL GOING
TO FIND A WAY TO GET HER BACK.
Izzy:
HEY!
I KNOW WHERE SORA IS!
Izzy:
I THINK DATAMON ONLY PRETENDED
TO TAKE HER AWAY.
IN REALITY, THEY'VE BEEN
RIGHT HERE THE WHOLE TIME.
ARE YOU SAYING
THEY'RE STILL IN THE PYRAMID?!
YES.
I'VE DISCOVERED THAT WAY DOWN
BELOW THE PYRAMID
THERE'S A SECRET ROOM...
AND I JUST KNOW
THAT'S WHERE HE IS HOLDING THEM.
HE'S FOUND THE PERFECT
HIDING PLACE
RIGHT UNDER ETEMON'S NOSE.
NOT A BAD PLACE,
AS LONG AS HE ISN'T SNEEZING.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A WAY IN!
I DON'T CARE
WHAT I'VE GOT TO DO,
I'M GOING TO FIND THAT ROOM...
I'M GOING TO BRING SORA BACK!
GUYS, I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND
IF YOU'D RATHER WAIT HERE.
ENOUGH WITH THE GUILT TRIP...
I'M COMING WITH YA!
REMEMBER THE OLD SAYING, TAI.
THERE'S NO "I" IN TEAM.
CAN I COME, TOO, IF I'M BRAVE?
SURE...ALL RIGHT THEN,
NOW...
LET'S GO GET SORA--TOGETHER!
Sora:
HAVE I BEEN DREAMING?
THIS ISN'T MY BEDROOM,
WHERE AM I?
( with alarm )
BIYOMON!
IT ISN'T A DREAM!
NOOOOO...!
( moaning with fear ) Datamon:
DON'T BE ALARMED, MY DEAR.
SHE'S SIMPLY EXHAUSTED
FROM ALL THE EXCITEMENT.
SHE'LL BE FINE WHEN I USE HER
IN MY PLAN TO DESTROY ETEMON.
BIYOMON CAN'T DIGIVOLVE
WITHOUT ME
AND I'D RATHER BE STUCK IN
A SEWER FILLED WITH RATS
THAN HELP YOU!
GOOD THEN,
I'LL REMEMBER YOU SAID THAT.
Sora:
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO TO ME?!
Datamon:
JUST REMAIN CALM!
OOHHH!
GET ME OFF THIS THING!
WE'VE JUST STARTED.
HUH!
HEY, WHAT'S HAPPENING
OVER THERE?
RELAX, I'M JUST MAKING
A COPY OF YOU.
WHA...
YOU SEE, I BELIEVE
BIYOMON'S POWER
HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH YOU, MY DEAR,
BUT RATHER WHOEVER HAPPENS
TO BE IN POSSESSION
OF THAT FANCY DIGIVICE
YOU SO PROUDLY WEAR.
YOU WILL NEVER BE ABLE TO
COMMAND, BIYOMON.
PERHAPS NOT... BUT WE'LL SEE
IF AN EXACT REPLICA OF YOU
CAN DO IT.
THIS JUST
CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
I COULD BE WRONG.
WHEN I FOUGHT
THE BEAST BEFORE
ETEMON DESTROYED
ALL OF MY MEMORY CIRCUITS
EXCEPT THOSE OF THE FIGHT.
FROM THAT MOMENT ON
I VOWED I'D HAVE MY REVENGE.
AND I WILL HAVE IT
WITH THE HELP
OF YOUR DIGI-PARTNER.
BUT ENOUGH OF THIS SMALL TALK.
THE MOMENT OF TRUTH
HAS ARRIVED!
IZZY:
BOY, WITH SO MANY
OF THE DIGIMON
SURROUNDING THE PYRAMID
LIKE THIS,
THERE IS JUST NO WAY
WE CAN GET IN THERE
WITHOUT SOMEBODY SEEING US.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHY WE'RE GOING
TO BE ACTING AS DECOYS.
RIGHT.
NOW TAI, WHEN THE ENEMY STARTS
CHASING AFTER US
YOU AND AGUMON HAVE GOT TO GET
INSIDE THERE QUICKLY
WITHOUT BEING SEEN
BY ANYONE...GOT IT?
UH-HUH.
YOU DO HAVE DIRECTIONS
FOR ME, DON'T YOU?
YEAH, JUST ONE MORE THING.
WHY DO I WANT TO THROW UP
EVERY TIME YOU SAY THAT?
OKAY NOW,
TO ENTER THE SECRET ROOM
YOU HAVE TO TAKE
A HIDDEN PASSAGE.
BUT THERE'S ANOTHER ELECTRIFIED
WALL TO GET PAST...
JUST LIKE THE ROOM
DATAMON WAS IN.
( gasping )
I CAN'T MOVE.
Agumon:
DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN MAKE IT, TAI?
I DON'T CARE
WHAT THE WALL IS!
I'M GOING THROUGH!
Joe:
NOW TRY NOT TO DO
ANYTHING STUPID
AND STAY OUT OF UNNECESSARY
TROUBLE, TAI.
REMEMBER, THE IMPORTANT THING
IS SAVING SORA.
Izzy:
AND YOU GUYS TRY NOT TO DO
ANYTHING STUPID EITHER.
IF YOU RUN INTO ETEMON
JUST TURN AROUND
AND RUN THE OTHER WAY.
YOU GOT THAT, T.K.?
WHOEVER DOESN'T
COME BACK ALIVE
IS GONNA BE IN
A LOT OF TROUBLE.
GOT IT?
Tai:
IF THIS WORKS, EVERYBODY HAS TO
GET THEIR PART EXACTLY RIGHT.
THEY'RE COMING
OUT OF THE PYRAMID.
Matt:
TAKE COVER EVERYONE.
BATTLE POSITIONS!
THANKS, MIMI.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
GET DOWN.
Ikkakumon:
HARPOON TORPEDO.
( explosion )
( whimpering with fear )
EARTHQUAKE...
GET UNDER THE DESK!
All:
OH NO!
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
IKKAKUMON IS BOMBING US!
WELL BOMB HIM BACK...UHH!
GRRR...
( screaming in fear )
ALRIGHT,
BE BRAVE.
( all roaring )
Joe:
MAYBE TOMORROW.
( large explosion )
Matt:
OKAY, GARURUMON, LET'S GO!
HOWLING BLASTER!
(all screaming in chaos )
WE MUST
DESTROY THEM ALL!
ALRIGHT YOU CLOWNS,
COME ON.
FOLLOW US!
LOOK BOSS, WE DID IT...
THEY'RE RUNNING AWAY!
WHAT...
I DON'T GET IT!
THEY SHOULD BE GIVING US
EVERYTHING THEY GOT!
I DON'T LIKE
THE SMELL OF THIS.
IT WASN'T ME, BOSS.
BUT LISTEN,
DATAMON DID SOMETHING
TO JAM UP THE NETWORK
AND WE CAN'T
FIND ANY EVIDENCE
AS TO WHERE THE TARGET
MIGHT BE.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOUR FACE
TILL YOU FIND THEM!
BUT BOSS--
NOW DON'T BUG ME
WITH THE LITTLE DETAILS...
JUST DO IT!
I'M GOING TO RID OF ALL THEM
TROUBLE-MAKERS, TODAY!
I HOPE JOE AND MATT
MAKE IT OKAY.
COME ON IZZY...
LET'S MOVE OUT!
ROGER.
HE FORGOT HIS NAME.
WE'LL BE BACK.
Izzy:
WHEN YOU GET TO THE WALL
JUST KEEP RUNNING!
Tai:
GOTCHA.
Izzy:
SO FAR SO GOOD.
THIS IS THE RIGHT WAY--
I'M SURE.
( panting )
OHH!
THE PASSAGE IS BLOCKED.
IT'S A DEAD END.
NOT NECESSARILY.
TRY THAT DOOR OVER THERE.
IT'S CLEAR...
LETS GO.
HEY, DID YOU NOTICE ANYTHING
ON THE MIDDLE MONITOR?
YEAH, YOU'RE ATTRACTING
FLIES AGAIN!
HUH...HMM.
JOE AND MATT
NEED OUR HELP.
PLEASE PALAMON,
YOU'VE GOT TO DIGIVOLVE NOW!
NOW, REMEMBER T.K.,
DON'T MOVE.
Etemon:
SUMMON THE DARK NETWORK.
( roaring )
UHH!
IT'S TIME TO GO.
Etemon:
AH, YOU'RE BECOMING
A NUISANCE, SON.
OF COURSE...
IT'S BECAUSE I'M A TEENAGER.
I HAVE TO ADMIT, IT'S BEEN
A LOT OF FUN
TOYING WITH YOU,
BUT NOW PLAYTIME'S OVER
IT'S THE END OF THE LINE
FOR YOU AND YOUR GOAT, BABY.
Datamon:
YOUR FRIENDS ARE VERY
PERCEPTIVE, MY DEAR.
IT'S SEEMS THAT THEY HAVE
ALREADY DISCOVERED
THAT I'M HOLDING YOU PRISONER
IN THIS PYRAMID.
WHAT WAS THAT EXPLOSION?
Datamon:
THERE'S A FEROCIOUS BATTLE
RAGING OUTSIDE,
AND SEVERAL OF YOUR FRIENDS
HAVE EVEN MANAGED
TO ENTER THE PYRAMID.
MY FRIENDS?
SEE LOOK,
I GOT THEM ON TAPE.
YOU SAID IT WAS FLIES.
FAST FORWARD.
Ikkakumon:
I HATE RUNNING AWAY.
Both:
AHH!
( grunting )
HA HA HA!
HOWLING BLASTER!
EEE-YAAA!
NEEDLE SPRAY!
EEE-YA-EEE-YA...!
Etemon:
IS THAT THE BEST YOU GOT?
I'VE SEEN SHARPER NEEDLES
IN GRANNY'S KNITTING BAG.
I THINK WE NEED
A NEW PLAN.
Etemon:
WELL COME ON,
LITTLE PLAYMATES.
SHOW ME WHAT YOU'VE GOT.
GRRRR!
GARURUMOM!
AHH--UHNGH!
Etemon:
( grunting and groaning )
IKKAKUMON, GET UP!
( loud grunting noises )
E-HUY!
UNGH!
OH-NEEDLE SPRAY!
HUH!
UHH-AHH!
TOGEMON!
I WOULD LIKE TO CLOSE THE SHOW
WITH A TUNE
THAT IS CURRENTLY
NUMBER ONE ON THE CHARTS-
IT GOES SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
( singing badly )
( All groaning and moaning )
I JUST CAN'T STAND IT!
( loud groaning )
Mimi:
( crying )
Both:
OH, NO!
AND DON'T FORGET TO
TIP YOUR WAITRESS.
Gazimon:
ETEMON, I'VE DISCOVERED
THE WHEREABOUTS
OF THE OTHER CHILDREN, SIR.
THEY ARE INSIDE THE PYRAMID.
WHY WOULD THEY?...
UNLESS DATAMON
WAS STILL INSIDE THE PYRAMID.
( screaming )
DATAMON IS SMARTER
THAN I THOUGHT,
BUT NOT NEARLY AS SMART
AS ME.
HUH...NOW WHERE DID
ALL THOSE OTHERS GO?
WHAT'S A LEGEND GOTTA DO
TO KEEP AN AUDIENCE, BABY?
WELL, IT DOESN'T MATTER...
I'LL JUST DESTROY THE ONES
IN THE PYRAMID FIRST,
AND THEN I'LL COME BACK
FOR THE REST OF THEM LATER.
UH-HUH-HUH.
HI-YA, MOVE,
YOU GOOD FOR NOTHING SLOWPOKE.
HE'S GOT
A LOT OF ANGER.
AND HE SURE
GETS MAD EASILY.
( all laughing )
BUT WHAT ABOUT TAI?
OH THAT'S RIGHT...
SOMETHING TELLS ME
HE'S NOT LAUGHING
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
Tai:
LOOKS LIKE THE GAZIMON
HAVE FIGURED OUT WE'RE HERE.
AND WE'RE SO CLOSE
TO THE ROOM...
I THINK THE MAIN PASSAGE
THAT LEADS
TO THE PRIVATE ENTRANCE
TO ETEMON'S LAB
IS AT THE BOTTOM
OF THIS STAIRWAY.
LET'S MOVE.
AHH!
( screaming )
NOW, BEFORE I CANCEL YOU
LIKE BAD SITCOM,
DIRECT ME TO DATAMON.
GO FIND SORA!
TENTOMON - DIGIVOLVE!
( celestial sounds )
TENTOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
KABUTERIMON!
Tai:
HOLD HIM, KABUTERIMON.
HEY!
( panting from fear )
OH, GREAT!
Agumon:
AN ELECTRIC WALL.
I COULD BREAK
THROUGH IT, TAI.
I'LL DO IT, AGUMON.
ARE YOU SURE?
NOT EXACTLY...
BUT IF I DON'T
DO THIS ON MY OWN,
HERE AND NOW,
I MIGHT NEVER BE ABLE TO.
A MAN MUST FACE HIMSELF
BEFORE HE COULD HIS ENEMIES.
I THINK I UNDERSTAND, TAI.
GO FOR IT!
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
YEEAAA!!
IT'S A FAKE.
YIPPPEEE!
( loud scream )
SO WE MEET AGAIN.
AGUMON!
( celestial sounds )
AGUMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
GREYMON!
TAI, BREAK THROUGH TO SORA.
GOOD LUCK, GREYMON.
( groaning )
SORA,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
SORA!- SPEAK TO ME.
Biyomon:
THAT'S NOT SORA!
THAT'S JUST A COPY!
HERE, TAI.
Datamon:
AND NOW THE COPY IS FINISHED.
I WILL GIVE HER
THE MAGIC CREST,
AND SHE WILL BECOME
THE NEW SORA,
AND DO WHATEVER
I REQUIRE OF HER.
THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK,
YOU PILE OF JUNK.
NO!
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?!
I CAN NOT PERMIT A MERE BOY
TO SPOIL MY PLANS FOR VENGEANCE.
I'M COMING, SORA!
AHHH!
( grunting )
BIYOMON!
Datamon:
THAT IS THE CENTER
OF ETEMON'S DARK POWER NETWORK.
ANYTHING SUCKED IN THERE
IS LOST TO ALL ETERNITY.
AND SINCE I HAVE
NO USE FOR THE ORIGINAL
I'LL SIMPLY GET RID OF IT.
TAI, THE CREST!
YES, THE CREST IS THE MEANS
BY WHICH YOU MAY SAVE
THE MAIDEN'S LIFE.
IF YOU GIVE IT
TO ME, IMMEDIATELY!
WHY DON'T YOU GO TELL
ETEMON YOUR SAD STORY,
BECAUSE WE'RE NOT INTERESTED!
NO, WAIT!
NOT SCARED ARE YA, DATAMON!
Sora:
Biyomon!
BIYOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
BIRDRAMON!
Datamon:
STAY BACK
YOU BLASTED CROW!
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
THOSE ARE MINE!
DON'T YOU WORRY, TIN-HEAD
I'LL PLAY WITH YOU.
OOOH!
( moaning with fear )
WE MADE IT!
I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D SEE YOU AGAIN.
HEY, HERE COME THE OTHERS.
( cheering )
WE'RE ALL HERE!
WE'RE COMING!
WERE COMING!
WITHOUT THE CREST,
THIS THING IS USELESS.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO DISMANTLE YOU
THE SAME WAY YOU DISMANTLED
YOUR LITTLE PLAYMATE,
YOU MISERABLE PILE OF BOLTS.
THE FLOOR!
HUH?!
( grunting )
LET GO!!
IF I'M GOING DOWN
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME!
JUST TRY THESE!
I WON'T SAY IT AGAIN--
LET GO OF ME,
OR I'M GOING TO OPEN YOU UP
LIKE A CAN OF BEANS!
THOSE WERE COMPUTER VIRUSES
I DROPPED INTO THE BLACK PIT
THAT WILL KEEP GROWING
AND ABSORB ALL THE DARK ENERGY
OF OUR COSMOS--
INCLUDING YOURS, FOOL!
YOU KNOW
HOW I HATE BUGS!
( groaning and screaming )
( screaming )
UH-HUH!
AHHH!
( grunting )
LET ME OUT OF HERE!
Joe:
WHAT HAPPENED BACK THERE?
Sora:
LOOK AT THE PYRAMID.
Tai:
IT'S DISINTEGRATING!
( evil laughter )
LET'S SEE A SHOW OF HANDS,
HOW MANY ACTUALLY
MISSED ME, HUH?
( all gasping )
WHAT'S WITH THIS GUY?
Etemon:
I TOLD YOU I'D COME BACK
AND TAKE MY REVENGE ON YOU-
YOU DIDN'T BELIEVE ME, DID YOU?
METEOR WING!
ELECTRO-SHOCKER!
( explosion )
Etemon:
HEY, THAT WAS PRETTY GOOD.
I GIVE IT A 9.6
NOW THEN, ARE YOU READY
FOR A FAST BALL?
YAA!
( loud bang )
THAT ONE'S HEADED
RIGHT FOR THE SPHINX!
AHH, THE SPHINX MELTED.
MELTING DOESN'T
EVEN DESCRIBE IT.
WE'VE TRIED EVERYTHING
AND NOTHING CAN STOP HIM...
I GUESS THIS IS THE END.
I WAS HOPING
TO SKIP ALGEBRA,
BUT NOT LIKE THIS.
NO, I'M NOT READY TO SURRENDER
TO ETEMON JUST YET!
COMING GREYMON?
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
Etemon:
WHAT DO WE GOT HERE SPORTS FANS?
A NEW BATTER STEPS TO THE PLATE.
I'M NOT AFRAID OF YOU,
YOU BIG BLOW HARD.
COME DOWN HERE
AND FIGHT LIKE A MON!
Mimi:
TAI, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
YOU ARE BRAVE-
I LIKE THAT.
DON'T WORRY GREYMON,
I'M STAYING WITH YOU!
TAI, YOUR COURAGE IS GIVING ME
EVEN GREATER STRENGTH.
I CAN DIGIVOLVE!
( celestial sounds )
GREYMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
METAL-GREYMON!!!
( large roar )
( roar )
( evil laughter ) LOOKIE HERE--
A FULLY EVOLVED DIGIMON!
WELL, I CAN HANDLE HIM, TOO.
JUST WATCH ME, KIDS.
METAL-GREYMON?
IT WAS THE POWER
FROM THE CREST.
METAL-GREYMON USES HIS OWN BODY
AS A WEAPON IN BATTLE.
HIS MOST LETHAL INSTRUMENT IS
THE GIGA-DESTROYER!
ETEMON IS EVERYBODY'S ENEMY!
USE THE POWER OF THE CREST!
IS THERE NO END
TO YOUR STUPIDITY?
MAYBE I COULD PUT
AN END TO IT FOR YOU.
YAH!
IT WAS JUST A JOKE.
( roar )
FINISH HIM NOW
WHILE WE HAVE THE POWER!
BACK OFF, BABY.
Etemon:
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?!
DON'T YOU KNOW THE RULES?
NO HEAD BUTTING ALLOWED.
GRRRR!
HE'S GLOWING...
I WISH MY HAIR COULD DO THAT.
IT'S THE CREST POWER.
Etemon:
DON'T DESTROY ME!
I'VE GOT TOO MUCH TALENT!!
GIGA-BLASTER!
NOOOOO!!
( all gasping )
YOU MUST NOT DEFEAT ME--
I'M JUST TOO IMPORTANT
TO DIEEEEEE....
( screaming )
DON'T LET GO OF ME,
METAL-GREYMON!
( both screaming )
All:
TAI!
T.K.:
WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM?
COME BACK!
OH...
Tai:
WHERE AM I?
WHO ARE ALL THESE PEOPLE?
KOROMON!
IM - I'M HOME.