DURING THE FALL, WE WERE
SEPARATED FROM IZZY AND TAI.
WE DISCOVERED THE NUMAMON
WERE BEING FORCED WARUMANZIMON
TO CREATE THE ENERGY
FOR THE CITY ABOVE.
AS KARI
STARTED FEELING BETTER,
THIS STRANGE LIGHT APPEARED
AND MADE US DIGIS
MUCH STRONGER.
WE WERE ABLE
TO FREE THE NUMAMON.
TAI AND IZZY
RAN INTO MACHINEDRAMON,
AND HE CHASED THEM
RIGHT INTO US.
THE NUMAMON
TRIED TO STOP HIM,
BUT THEY WERE NO MATCH.
USING THE POWER
OF THE LIGHT,
WARGREYMON WAS FINALLY
ABLE TO DESTROY MACHINEDRAMON.
I'M JUST GLAD
KARI'S OKAY NOW.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
BOY, JUST WHEN YOU THINK
IT CAN'T GET ANY WEIRDER.
IT'S LIKE THE WHOLE CITY
IS MOVING OUT OF TOWN.
AND I THOUGHT IT WAS
TOUGH PACKING FOR CAMP.
TAI MUST HAVE DEFEATED
ANOTHER DARK MASTER.
THERE CAN'T BE
MANY OF THEM MANY LEFT.
WE'RE ALMOST HOME FREE.
YOU THINK SO, HUH? THE TOUGHEST
ONE'S STILL OUT THERE.
PIEDMON --
THE WORST OF THE WORST.
AH, HE'S THE DARKEST
OF THE DARK MASTERS.
WELL, RAIN ON OUR PARADE,
WHY DON'T YOU?
THEY'RE RIGHT. WE'LL
NEED ALL THE HELP WE CAN GET.
I WONDER IF SUPERHEROES
ARE LISTED IN THE PHONE BOOK.
LET'S FIND
SOME FRIENDS, MIMI.
Piedmon: HA HA HA.
THAT'S RIGHT.
ROUND UP AS MANY AS YOU WANT.
THE MORE, THE MERRIER.
IT'S NICE
HAVING FRIENDS AROUND
TO SHARE YOUR LAST MOMENTS.
HA HA HA HA HA.
JOE, WHY IS IT WE'RE
ALWAYS WALKING UPHILL?
YEAH! IT'S FREEZING!
HEY, DO YOU MIND?
I'M STARTING TO
GET NUMB BACK THERE.
GIVE ME A LITTLE ROOM.
YOU, TOO, YOU WALKING BARBECUE.
THE WALKING UPHILL
I CAN DEAL WITH,
BUT I SURE COULD USE
A PAIR OF EARPLUGS.
[ PANTS ]
OHH!
I'M HUNGRY, I'M TIRED,
AND MY FEET HURT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO
DO WHEN YOU'RE LIKE THIS.
PRINCESS MIMI
JUST SAID SHE WAS HUNGRY.
DON'T WORRY. WE'LL BE BACK
WITH FOOD BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
DON'T PUT YOURSELF OUT,
BUT A CHILI DOG WITH FRIES
WOULD BE GREAT.
THE PRINCESS WILL BE
WANTING SOMETHING TO DRINK.
THAT'S RIGHT.
DON'T YOU WORRY,
PRINCESS MIMI.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
NO, WAIT, COME BACK!
NOT A BAD IDEA.
I THINK I'LL TAG ALONG.
WOW, EVERYBODY'S
BEING SO NICE, SO SWEET.
IT MUST BE BECAUSE
OF YOUR CHARMING PERSONALITY.
SOMETHING TELLS ME
WE SHOULD JUST NOD OUR HEADS
AND GO ALONG.
YEAH, RIGHT.
COME ON, ADMIT IT, JOE.
SAY IT, SHE'S CHARMING.
SHE'S NOT CHARMING --
I MEAN, SHE IS!
I'M NOT GOING TO
HAVE THIS CONVERSATION!
Both: HA HA HA HA.
YOO-HOO! WE'RE BACK!
Mimi:
I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
WOW! HEY, MY FAVORITE!
OH, THIS
ROOT BEER'S WARM.
NOT FOR LONG.
HOW'S THAT?
THERE WE GO.
COME ON,
GET IT WHILE IT'S HOT!
OKAY, OKAY,
I'LL ADMIT IT.
GUESS YOU GUYS
ARE KIND OF HANDY.
[ SNORING ]
JOE, LET ME
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE A DOCTOR
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO BE.
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
TRY TELLING THAT TO DAD.
IT'S YOUR LIFE, BRO.
YOU HAVE TO LIVE IT.
YOU HAVE TO FOLLOW
YOUR OWN PATH.
UHH!
HEY, OGREMON.
4 PLUS 4 IS 7 --
HEY!
TAKE A REST.
I'LL STAND GUARD
FOR A WHILE.
YOU?
ARE YOU SURE YOU
CAN HANDLE IT, LITTLE GUY?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I CAN HANDLE IT FINE!
YOU CAN'T EVEN HANDLE
COMBING YOUR HAIR,
BUT I COULD USE A BREAK.
JIM'S RIGHT.
I'M A DOORMAT.
GOOD FOR A LAUGH,
A JOKE.
YEAH, GOOD OL' JOE.
YOU CAN ALWAYS RELY ON HIM
TO FALL INTO THE MUD.
NOT ANYMORE. IT'S TIME
FOR A BRAND-NEW JOE.
Piedmon: HOW DELIGHTFULLY
ENTERTAINING THIS IS. I ALWAYS GET SO EXCITED
BEFORE TRAGEDY STRIKES.
THANK YOU, NUMAMON.
WE'LL NEVER FORGET YOU.
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE
IN OUR HEARTS AND OUR MEMORIES.
AND DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL MAKE SURE THAT YOU
GET REBORN IN PRIMARY VILLAGE.
EVER NOTICE HOW WE'RE
ALWAYS WALKING UPHILL?
OKAY, NICE VIEW,
BUT WHAT ARE WE LOOKING FOR?
THAT, OVER THERE!
IF THAT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE A BAD GUY'S HANGOUT,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT DOES.
Piedmon: HMM, REMARKABLE
LITTLE SPECIMENS.
I'M REALLY RATHER EMBARRASSED
THAT THEY MADE IT THIS FAR.
OH, PLEASE, PLEASE,
LORD PIEDMON,
LET ME PUNISH THEM.
VERY WELL,
BUT TRY TO MAKE IT QUICK
AND RELATIVELY PAINFUL.
Mimi: OKAY, I'M RESTED
AND READY TO WORK OFF
THAT SNACK,
SO LET'S GO, GO, GO!
YOU KNOW, WHEN MIMI'S
IN A GOOD MOOD,
IT'S HARD TO
NOT BE HAPPY, TOO.
Mimi: IT'S JUST MY LITTLE
GIFT TO THE WORLD.
YEAH.
YOU'RE AWFULLY QUIET, JOE.
WHAT'S WRONG?
NOTHING.
I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
OH, NO, JOE!
THIS IS AWFUL.
Joe: IT LOOKS LIKE AN OLD
"TWILIGHT ZONE" EPISODE.
I TOLD YOU
NOT TO EXPECT TOO MUCH.
Mimi: THE COLOR
IS ALL MISSING.
Joe: PRETTY DEPRESSING,
UNLESS YOU'RE A FAN
OF CHARCOAL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE ANYBODY
WOULD DO
SUCH A TERRIBLE THING,
SMASHING ALL THOSE
POOR, DEFENSELESS DIGIEGGS.
IT'S TERRIBLE.
HUH?
Mimi:
WHAT IS IT, JOE?
I HEARD SOMETHING.
[ HARMONICA PLAYS ]
OVER THERE!
JOE, WAIT!
WAS THAT A HARMONICA?
YOU THINK IT'S...
MATT!
WHERE ARE THEY HEADED?
HEY, WAIT FOR US!
THAT'S IT.
WE'RE READY.
THAT'S GREAT, IZZY,
BUT READY FOR WHAT?
HANG ON A SECOND
AND YOU'LL SEE.
OKAY, ANDROMON,
SHOW US YOUR STUFF.
ENGAGE HEAT CONDUCTION.
I DON'T GET
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
Izzy: IT'S REALLY
RATHER SIMPLE.
ANDROMON ACQUIRES
GEOTHERMAL ENERGY
DIRECTLY FROM THE GROUND.
WAY COOL!
HEY, THAT'S SPIRAL MOUNTAIN,
ISN'T IT?
THIS IS LIKE HAVING
OUR OWN PORTABLE MICROWAVE.
THERE, LOOK, THAT'S
WHERE WE ARE RIGHT NOW,
RIGHT ON TOP.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
HOW DID WE GET UP THERE?
I'M SURE GLAD
I CAN'T SEE DOWN.
I DON'T LIKE
HIGH PLACES.
IT'S LIKE CHUUMON SAID.
THE MOST POWERFUL
DARK MASTERS
LIVE WAY ON TOP
OF SPIRAL MOUNTAIN.
SEE? I TOLD YOU
WE WERE CLOSE.
WE'LL GIVE YOU
A MEDAL LATER.
INTRUDER WARNING!
INTERLOPER DETECTED!
HUH?
HA HA HA HA HA!
AH, HA HA HA.
YOU PILE
OF RECYCLED SCRAP METAL,
YOU SPOILED MY ENTRANCE.
WE SHOULD HAVE KNOWN THERE'D
BE A WELCOMING COMMITTEE.
SHE LOOKS
LIKE A WITCH.
SHE'S WORSE.
SHE'S ONE OF PIEDMON'S
NIGHTMARE SOLDIERS.
NO HELLOS?
WELL,
I'M SURE YOU'RE TIRED.
YOU POOR THINGS,
YOU NEED A REST,
AH, A NICE LONG REST.
OH, YEAH?
KOROMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
KOROMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
AGUMON!
PEPPER BREATH!
POINT!
MM!
AAH --
OOH! OOH!
AGUMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
PATAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
ANGEMON!
BIYOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
BIRDRAMON!
TENTOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
KABUTERIMON!
GATOMOM DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
ANGEWOMAN!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HA HA HA HA HA!
YOU'VE JUST MADE MY JOB
A LOT EASIER.
DARKNESS WAVE!
Both: AAH!
AAH!
LIGHTNING BLADE! UHH!
YA!
ELECTRO-SHOCKER!
METEOR WING!
HA HA HA HA HA.
ARE WE JUST PRETENDING?
LET ME KNOW WHEN YOU'RE READY.
HAND OF FATE!
MM!
CELESTIAL ARROW!
UHH! GRRR!
HA!
[ GASPS ]
AAH! UHH!
IT'S MY TURN!
NO, WAIT.
WE'LL KEEP YOU IN RESERVE.
LET ME WARP-DIGEVOLVE.
I CAN TAKE CARE OF THIS
BLACK-AND-WHITE NIGHTMARE.
IZZY, WHAT'S YOUR DIGIMON
ANALYZER SAY ABOUT HER?
LADY DEVIMON -- PROGRAMMED
TO BE THE ULTIMATE
FULLY-DIGEVOLVED
FIGHTING SOLDIER,
SHE SERVES AS GATEKEEPER
AND BODYGUARD
FOR THE LAST DARK MASTER.
SERIOUSLY NASTY.
WE'VE GOT TO
DO THIS RIGHT.
SORA, YOU AND T.K.
TAKE ANGEMON AND BIRDRAMON,
FIND MATT,
AND BRING HIM BACK.
YOU WANT US TO LEAVE
IN THE MIDDLE OF A FIGHT?
UHH!
GO!
WE'LL MANAGE HERE.
WE'LL HAVE TO.
AND EVEN
IF WORST COMES TO WORST,
WE ALWAYS HAVE
OUR TRUMP CARD -- WARGREYMON.
OH, I'M
A TRUMP CARD, HUH?
THE TIME HAS COME
TO STOP ACTING LIKE KIDS.
WE'RE FACING THE LAST
OF THE DARK MASTERS.
PIEDMON.
RIGHT. WE DON'T KNOW
WHERE HE'LL STRIKE OR WHEN,
BUT IT WILL BE
SOMEWHERE CLOSE BY...
AND SOON.
AND HE'S STRONG.
WE KNOW THAT -- REAL STRONG.
THIS WON'T BE
JUST ANOTHER FIGHT.
THIS ONE'S FOR KEEPS.
WE'VE GOT
TO BE READY FOR HIM.
SO THAT'S WHY
YOU WANT US TO GO,
TO FIND MY BROTHER
AND BRING HIM BACK
BEFORE PIEDMON SHOWS UP.
YEAH, TAI'S LOOKING
AT THE BIG PICTURE.
IT'S NOT ABOUT THIS FIGHT,
BUT THE NEXT ONE, SEE?
SORT OF.
BASES LOADED, TWO OUT,
AND WE NEED A SLAM-DUNK.
HUH?
ALL WE'VE BEEN DOING
IS MEETING EACH THREAT,
BARELY HOLDING ON.
NOW WE'VE GOT TO PUT IT
ALL TOGETHER AS A TEAM.
THAT MEANS MATT, MIMI,
AND JOE, TOO.
WE'VE LET ENOUGH DIGIMON
SACRIFICE THEMSELVES FOR US.
IT'S OUR TURN NOW.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
CELESTIAL ARROW!
HA HA HA HA HA!
GO, ANGEMON!
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON, BIRDRAMON.
UHH!
OH, SORRY, BLONDIE.
HA HA HA HA HA.
GRRR!
SEE YOU SOON, TAI!
DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL FIND MATT
AND MIMI AND JOE,
AND BE BACK
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
TRY AND HURRY!
THIS IS KIND OF IMPORTANT.
I'LL DO THE BEST I CAN.
Piedmon:
WELL, WELL, LET'S JUST SEE HOW OUR LITTLE DRAMA
IS UNRAVELING. HA!
[ HARMONICA PLAYS ]
MM.
OH, SO IT WAS YOU.
WE THOUGHT
IT WAS SOMEONE ELSE.
YEAH, I'M SURE YOU DID.
IT'S ALWAYS THE SAME THING.
I'M JUST A CONSTANT SOURCE
OF DISAPPOINTMENT TO EVERYBODY.
HEY, HOW'S PATAMON
AND T.K.?
THEY ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. BOTH OF THEM WILL
BE REALLY HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
YEAH. NOT THAT
WE'RE NOT, OF COURSE.
YEAH, RIGHT. I'M SURE.
NICE TRY.
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU
COME ALONG WITH US?
HUH?
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO DEFEAT
THOSE CREEPY DARK MASTERS
ONCE AND FOR ALL,
AND FIX UP
PRIMARY VILLAGE, TOO.
WE NEED ALL THE FRIENDS
WE CAN GET.
I KNOW WE DON'T
LOOK LIKE MUCH,
BUT MAYBE WITH YOUR HELP,
WE CAN DO IT.
TAKE ON THE DARK MASTERS?
I THINK I'LL PASS.
I MAY BE DOWN,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO BE OUT.
FOR YOUR INFORMATION,
WE'VE TAKEN THEM ON.
IN FACT, WE'VE ALREADY
DEFEATED MOST OF THEM.
T.K. AND PATAMON
HAVE REALLY BEEN INCREDIBLE.
T.K. AND PATAMON?
MM!
THOSE SWEET KIDS
ARE MIXING IT UP
WITH THE DARK MASTERS?
OKAY, IF THEY'RE CRAZY ENOUGH
TO FIGHT THEM,
THEN I AM, TOO.
YOU TWISTED MY ARM.
HA HA HA HA HA.
FRANKLY,
YOU GUYS ARE LUCKY
TO HAVE GOTTEN THIS FAR
WITHOUT ME.
OH, IS THAT RIGHT?
BY THE WAY, WHERE'D YOU
GET THAT HARMONICA?
THIS THING?
I FOUND IT ON THE BEACH.
SOMEBODY
MUST HAVE DROPPED IT.
CAN I TAKE A LOOK AT IT?
OH, YEAH.
IT'S DEFINITELY MATT'S.
THAT MEANS HE MUST BE
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE,
OR HE WAS.
YOU THINK HE
MIGHT HAVE GONE ACROSS?
THAT'S A LONG WAY
TO SWIM.
NOW THAT
YOU MENTION IT,
I SAW SOMEBODY
CROSS THE WATER LAST NIGHT.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
ONE OF THOSE NIGHTMARE SOLDIERS.
THEY PROBABLY WOULDN'T
BE USING A BOAT
SHAPED LIKE A SWAN.
IT WAS A SWAN?
THAT SETTLES IT.
IT HAD TO HAVE BEEN MATT.
I CAN JUST PICTURE IT NOW.
LISTEN, MIMI,
YOU'VE GOT A LOT
OF FRIENDS NOW.
WILL YOU BE OKAY
IF GOMAMON AND I
GO OFF FOR A WHILE?
HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
GO WHERE?
I DON'T KNOW. I GUESS
WHEREVER'S MATT'S GONE TO.
OKAY, I'LL COME WITH YOU
AND HELP YOU FIND HIM.
NOT THIS TIME.
JUST GOMAMON CAN GO.
COME ON, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WE EACH HAVE OUR OWN PATH
TO FOLLOW.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
TAI KNOWS
WHAT HE'S DOING.
HE KNOWS WHERE HE FITS IN,
AND SO DO YOU.
SO DO THE OTHERS,
BUT I DON'T.
I KNOW WE'RE IN FOR
THE FIGHT OF OUR LIVES.
PART OF ME KNOWS
I SHOULD STAY AND HELP,
BUT I-I WANT YOU
TO COUNT ON ME.
IF I'M UNRELIABLE,
THEN GOMAMON
CAN'T FULLY DIGEVOLVE.
WE'RE LIKE CIRCUS CLOWNS.
WE JUST GET IN THE WAY.
YOU KNOW IT'S TRUE.
I'M GOING TO
FIGURE THIS OUT.
THEY DON'T CALL ME
"OLD RELIABLE" FOR NOTHING.
THEY DON'T.
I'LL IGNORE THAT.
I THINK MATT WAS SEARCHING
FOR THE SAME THING
WHEN HE LEFT,
AND I WANT TO KNOW
IF HE FOUND IT
SOMEWHERE OUT THERE.
THEN AGAIN, IT MIGHT BE
A TOTAL WASTE OF TIME.
IT'S JUST AN IDEA.
IF YOU FEEL
THAT STRONGLY ABOUT IT,
IT'S THE RIGHT THING.
YOU SURE ABOUT THIS,
JOE?
LET THE KID
GO HIS OWN WAY.
I'M WITH YOU, BUDDY.
HE'S STRONGER
THAN HE LOOKS.
MM.
DARKNESS WAVE!
[ BATS SQUEAKING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
UHH!
OHH!
ROUND AND ROUND WE GO!
HA HA HA HA!
AAH!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
KABUTERIMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
MEGAKABUTERIMON.
NEVER DID LIKE
THAT BLEACHED LOOK.
AAH!
GOTCHA!
LET ME GO!
LET ME AT HER!
AHH!
UHH!
AAH!
WOW! LOOK AT THEM GO!
I KNOW I SHOULDN'T
WATCH THIS,
BUT I CAN'T
TAKE MY EYES OFF THEM.
GET HER, ANGEWOMAN!
KNOCK THAT
WITCH'S BLOCK OFF! GO!
OHH!
ENOUGH OF THIS!
AAH!
THIS GAME IS OVER!
YOU'RE GROUNDED, GOLDILOCKS!
BLACK WING!
UHH!
AAH!
YOU BROKE IT!
AH, SEND ME THE BILL.
[ GASPS ]
YOU'RE RIGHT,
LADY DEVIMON.
THIS GAME IS OVER.
NO!
NOT YET! DARKNESS --
HEAVEN'S CHARM!
AAH!
I'M MELTING!
♪ MONSTER FRIENDS
TO THE BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
YIPPEE!
UHH!
HA HA HA HA HA.
HOW'S MY BACK?
CAN YOU SEE ANYTHING?
I HOPE IT DIDN'T
LEAVE A SCAR.
TAI, YOU SEE WHAT I SEE?
IT'S HIM!
[ BOTH GASP ]
IT DOESN'T LOOK GOOD,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
PIEDMON.
Tai: THE LAST
OF THE DARK MASTERS.
THE GUY'S NOT EXACTLY
IN A HURRY, IS HE?
SUIT UP, AGUMON.
YOU'RE ON.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
AGUMON WARP-DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ WARP-DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
WARGREYMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HA HA HA HA HA!
I'M READY!
REMEMBER, HE'S STRONG.
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW STRONG.
NO PROBLEM.
AT THIS RATE,
I'M ONLY WORRIED
ABOUT DYING OF OLD AGE.
IT'S OKAY. THE LONGER
HE DRAWS THIS OUT,
THE BETTER FOR US.
NO OFFENSE, WARGREYMON,
BUT YOU CAN ONLY
HOLD HIM OFF FOR SO LONG.
WE'RE GOING TO NEED
EVERYBODY FOR THIS ONE --
T.K. AND SORA,
MIMI,
AND OUR DIGIMON ALLIES.
AND JOE.
AND MOST OF ALL...
MATT.
I SAY LET HIM
TAKE HIS TIME.
OKAY, OKAY,
BUT THIS WAITING
GETS ON MY NERVES.
HA HA HA HA HA.
ARE THE DIGIDESTINED
READY TO FACE PIEDMON,
THE MOST POWERFUL VILLAIN
IN THE DIGIWORLD?
TUNE IN TO THE NEXT
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS."