Tai:
SO LET ME BRING YOU
UP TO SPEED.
ME AND THE OTHER 6 KIDS
WERE KICKING BACK
AT SUMMER CAMP
WHEN A FREAK SNOWSTORM
HITS.
WE FIND THESE DIGIVICES
AND BAM!
THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW
WE'RE TRANSPORTED TO THIS
WHACKED-OUT ISLAND.
ONE BY ONE WE MAKE FRIENDS
WITH THESE CREATURES
WHO ARE KNOWN
AS DIGITAL MONSTERS
OR DIGIMON.
EVERYTHING WAS COOL
TILL KUWAGAMON SHOWED UP.
OUR NEW FRIENDS
SOMEHOW DIGIVOLVED
INTO BIGGER DIGIMON
AND SCARED HIM OFF--
OR SO WE THOUGHT.
TALK ABOUT
YOUR CLIFFHANGERS.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
FOX KIDS WORLDWIDE AND
THE U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGI ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE
THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
HEY! WHOA!
AAAAAH!
SORA!
IZZY!
T.K.!
AAAAH!
AAA-AAAH! AAAAH!
FISH NET!
All: AAAAH!
WOW,
THIS IS SOME RIDE.
WHAT? HEY, LOOK OUT!
All: AAAAAH!
NO!
HUH? [GASPS]
OH!
All: AAAAAH!
[GROANING]
I KNEW WE'D BE OK,
I WASN'T WORRIED.
WHAT WAS THAT,
A FLOATING FISH MARKET?
LUCKY FOR US,
THOSE FISH WERE HAVING
A SCHOOL REUNION.
HA HA!
HUH?
I'M KIDDING. THOSE FISH
ARE GOOD FRIENDS OF MINE
AND I JUST ASKED THEM
FOR A LIFT.
A-AND ALL THESE YEARS
I THOUGHT I WAS ALLERGIC
TO SEAFOOD.
THANK YOU, UH,
I GUESS
IT'S NOT BUKAMON?
GOMAMON NOW.
GOMAMON, HMM.
AND I GUESS
THAT YOU'RE NOT TOKOMON,
ARE YOU?
MM-MMM.
NOW I'M PATAMON.
IT'S ALL BECAUSE
WE DIGIVOLVED.
I DON'T THINK
THAT WORD'S
IN MY DICTIONARY.
SO DIGIVOLVING
IS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN THEY ADVANCE
TO THE NEXT LEVEL
AND BECOME
MORE POWERFUL
THAN BEFORE.
RIGHT.
ALL OF US DIGIVOLVE.
I WENT FROM
MOTIMON TO TENTOMON.
I DIGIVOLVED
FROM YOCOMON
TO BIYOMON.
FIRST, I WAS TSUNOMON,
THEN GABUMON.
AND I CHANGED
FROM TANEMON
TO PALMON.
AND ME, I WAS KOROMON.
I DIGIVOLVED INTO AGUMON.
MM-HMM.
WHEN YOU
DIGIVOLVED,
YOU CERTAINLY
GOT WAY BIGGER.
DOES THIS MEAN
YOU'RE SOMETHING
DIFFERENT NOW
OR ARE YOU
STILL DIGIMON?
DIGIMON,
BUT I NEEDED
YOUR HELP, TAI.
ME? FOR WHAT?
YOU SEE, DIGIVOLVING IS
A VERY DIFFICULT PROCESS.
IN ORDER TO BE SUCCESSFUL,
I HAD TO SHARE YOUR ENERGY.
REALLY?
I GUESS YOU GUYS
DON'T RUN ON BATTERIES.
SURE DON'T.
BUT HOW DO YOU
ACCESS MY ENERGY?
EVEN WE DON'T KNOW
EVERYTHING.
THANKS FOR MY
MAGICAL POWERS.
THE WHOLE THING
MAKES MY HEAD SPINNY.
SO I HELP YOU CHANGE.
THAT IS SO COOL.
YEP. SURE IS.
MY FOLKS WARNED ME
ABOUT STRANGERS.
I'M NOT A STRANGER, JOE.
I'M YOUR FRIEND FOR LIFE.
MMM.
OK, COME ON,
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
IF ONLY THERE WAS
A PAY PHONE NEARBY.
WE COULD CALL THE POLICE
OR FIRE DEPARTMENT
OR MY MOTHER.
BUT WE
DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE WE ARE.
BUT WE KNOW WHERE
WE STARTED--UP THERE
ON THAT MOUNTAIN.
I SAY WE FORGET
ABOUT GOING BACK AND
EXPLORE AROUND HERE.
I'M NOT EXPLORING
ANYWHERE.
I SAY WE STAY
RIGHT WHERE WE ARE.
YEAH, LET'S WAIT
FOR THAT GIANT BUG
TO COME GET US.
WE NEED TO FIND A ROAD
LEADING SOMEPLACE
TO GET AWAY FROM HERE.
HMM,
MATT'S RIGHT, BUT
WITHOUT A COMPASS,
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHICH WAY IS NORTH.
WAIT, I DO.
WELL,
WHICH WAY IS IT?
IT'S THE OPPOSITE
OF SOUTH.
I SHOULDN'T
WEAR THESE PANTS.
THEY RIDE UP WHEN I DO
A LOT OF WALKING.
YOU KNOW,
IF WE COULD GET BACK
TO WHERE WE WERE BEFORE,
WE MIGHT AT LEAST
FIND SOME CLUES
AS TO WHY WE'RE HERE
IN THIS PLACE.
WAIT! ARE THERE
MORE MONSTERS AROUND
LIKE THAT
BIG FLYING BEETLE?
YES,
INDEEDY.
ICK!
THOSE MONSTERS
DON'T SCARE ME.
ARE THERE HUMANS?
HUMANS?
OTHERS LIKE YOU?
MM-HMM.
YOU'RE THE FIRST EVER.
THERE'S NEVER BEEN
ANYTHING BUT DIGIMON.
SO, OK, YOU ARE ALL DIGIMON.
BUT WHAT ABOUT
THESE MONSTERS,
THEY'RE ALL DIGIMON, TOO?
IT'S CREEPY,
AND DANGEROUS,
AND WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN IT GETS DARK?
WHO SAYS IT EVER
GETS DARK HERE?
THAT PHENOMENON
WOULD BE UNNATURAL.
AND YOU
CALL THIS NATURAL?
WELL, WE'RE NOT GONNA
FIND OUT ANYTHING
BY SITTING AROUND HERE.
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
UP ON THAT CLIFF.
THAT'S WHERE
I SAW THE OCEAN.
THE OCEAN?
YEP. THERE MIGHT BE
A BOAT OR SOMETHING.
LET'S WATER-SKI HOME.
AH, FUNNY.
AT A TIME LIKE THIS,
I THINK WE'D BE
FAR BETTER OFF
JUST TO FIND A CAVE
AND HIDE.
WE KEEP OUR EYES OPEN,
AND WHEN A CAMP COUNSELOR
COMES--
HEY, JOE,
EVERYONE'S
LEAVING US.
WAIT FOR ME.
THESE TREES
ARE BEAUTIFUL.
YEAH, THEY'RE
REALLY DIFFERENT,
AND I JUST THOUGHT
THEY WERE
SUBTROPICAL.
WHATEVER THEY ARE,
THEY'RE AGGRAVATING
MY HAY FEVER.
HEY, JOE, IS THERE
ANYTHING YOU DON'T
COMPLAIN ABOUT?
[CHUCKLES]
DIGITAL MONSTERS.
EXACTLY WHO CAME UP
WITH THAT NAME ANYWAY?
JUST CALL US DIGIMON,
WE LIKE THAT.
I ONLY ASK, BECAUSE
YOUR COMPOSITION
ISN'T AT ALL
MACHINE-LIKE.
OH, REALLY?
HEY, WATCH IT!
SO, PATAMON,
CAN YOU REALLY FLY?
OF COURSE.
WOW, THAT'S COOL,
BUT YOU'RE GOING
THE WRONG WAY.
I'M FASTER THAN THAT.
WATCH.
WOULDN'T IT BE FASTER
TO WALK? HUH?
PALMON, I'VE BEEN
MEANING TO ASK,
WHO DOES YOUR HAIR?
IT'S NATURAL.
I WAKE UP IN THE
MORNING LIKE THIS.
WOW, MAYBE YOU CAN
LET ME WORK WITH IT.
DO YOU THINK YOU PUT
TOO MUCH EMPHASIS
ON APPEARANCE?
WELL, HONESTLY I'VE NEVER
REALLY THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
HONESTLY, I KIND
OF LIKE MY HAIR
THE WAY IT IS.
ONCE I GET BACK,
THIS IS GONNA MAKE
ONE GREAT STORY, YEP.
BUT, OF COURSE,
NOT A SINGLE SOUL
WILL EVER BELIEVE ME.
THAT KUWAGAMON
BACK THERE,
HE WAS HUGE.
AND HE'S NOT
THE ONLY ONE.
[SNIFFS] AHH,
NOTHING LIKE THE OCEAN.
HA HA, EVERYBODY
IN THE WATER!
T.K.: HEY, LET'S BUILD
A GIANT SAND CASTLE.
Mimi: OH, I FORGOT
MY BATHING SUIT.
Matt:
WAIT A MINUTE,
LISTEN, WHAT'S THAT?
A PHONE.
EITHER THAT
OR WE'RE ALL
HEARING THINGS.
[RING]
Joe: I TOLD YOU,
ALL WE NEEDED WAS A PHONE.
WE'RE SAVED!
[RING]
HUH?
WHY'D IT STOP
RINGING, TAI?
WRONG NUMBER?
Sora: WELL,
THAT'S BIZARRE.
T.K.:
MY THEORY IS ALIENS.
THEY'VE SET THESE PHONE
BOOTHS OUT AS A TRAP.
Matt: IF WE COULD FIND
A PLACE THAT DELIVERS,
LET'S ORDER PIZZA.
Mimi: WHATEVER YOU GET,
NO ANCHOVIES FOR ME.
Sora: THE QUESTION IS,
WHAT ARE THESE DOING HERE
AT THE BEACH?
SO PEOPLE CAN
CALL THEIR PARENTS
FOR A RIDE HOME.
PARENTS?
WHAT EXACTLY
IS A PARENTS?
THAT'S IT,
I'M OUTTA HERE.
DOES ANYBODY HAVE
ANY LOOSE CHANGE?
WHY?
OBVIOUSLY I'M GONNA
MAKE A PHONE CALL
TO GET SOME HELP.
AH, USE MY PHONE CARD.
THE ALIENS CAN BILL ME.
HERE.
MAYBE THERE'S A QUARTER
IN ONE OF THE SLOTS.
I'M CALLING DADDY.
I'M HOOKING UP
TO THE INTERNET.
I'M CALLING COLLECT.
DIBS ON BOOTH 4.
HEY, GUYS,
WAIT FOR ME. COME ON!
[RING]
HELLO? HEY, MOM,
IT'S ME.
Operator: AT THE TONE,
THE TIME WILL BE EXACTLY
45 MILES PER HOUR,
AND 90 SECONDS.
SOMETHING'S WRONG,
OR MOM'S FLIPPED.
Second Operator:
TOMORROW'S FORECAST
CALLS FOR CLEAR SKIES
WITH OCCASIONAL
ICE CREAM.
WHAT DO YOU WEAR
FOR THAT?
Third Operator:
THIS NUMBER ONLY EXISTS
IN YOUR IMAGINATION.
PLEASE HANG UP
AND DON'T CALL BACK.
WHAT PLANET DID I DIAL?
I'M TELLING YOU,
IT'S A TWISTED
ALIEN JOKE.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
THAT ONE OVER THERE?
I DON'T THINK
ITS ANY BETTER.
Fourth Operator:
TELEPHONES AREN'T WORKING
IN YOUR SERVICE AREA.
HANG UP AND
HAVE A NICE DAY.
HUMPH!
ANY LUCK?
NO.
WEIRD.
I GOT A STRANGE FEELING
ABOUT THIS.
MAYBE THIS ONE WILL.
Operator:
TO LEAVE A MESSAGE,
PRESS 1 NOW.
TO LEAVE
A FINGERPRINT,
PRESS 2 NOW.
$15 FOR THE NEXT
3 MINUTES.
OK, NEXT ONE.
VERY CURIOUS.
DOES JOE ALWAYS
BEHAVE LIKE THIS?
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
NO MATTER WHAT NUMBER
OR HOW MANY TIMES
HE DIALS,
THOSE PHONES
AREN'T GONNA WORK.
WELL, I'M GONNA KEEP
SEARCHING FOR A BOAT
OR SOMETHING.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
EVEN THOUGH WE CAN'T
CALL OUT OF HERE,
THERE'S ALWAYS A CHANCE
SOMEONE ELSE
MIGHT BE ABLE
TO CALL INTO US.
IT'S A WASTE OF TIME
DOING NOTHING
BUT SITTING HERE.
I'M GOING TO STAY HERE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE
AND SEE IF ANYONE CALLS.
BESIDES, EVERYONE
COULD USE A LITTLE REST.
[ALL GROANING]
AND I'M GETTING
PRETTY HUNGRY, TOO.
YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE
WE HAVEN'T EATEN
ANYTHING ALL DAY.
OK, BREAK TIME,
EVERYBODY.
DOES ANYBODY ELSE
HAVE ANY FOOD?
I THINK THE ONLY THING
I HAVE IS...HUH?
IT'S THAT GADGET THAT
FELL OUT OF THE SKY
AT CAMP.
I FORGOT ALL ABOUT
THOSE WEIRD GISMOS.
IF ANYBODY'S
GOT A PINK ONE,
I'LL TRADE.
WHAT ARE THEY ANYWAY?
WE WOULDN'T
HAVE THEM IF THEY
WEREN'T IMPORTANT.
IF I COULD
TAKE MINE APART...
UM, THAT IS,
AFTER I GET
SOMETHING TO EAT.
I'M REALLY FAMISHED.
WELL, THE ONLY THING
I'VE GOT IS MY
EMERGENCY SUPPLIES.
IT'S GOT A FIRST-AID KIT,
SOME BANDAGES,
AND SOME MEDICINE,
BUT THAT'S ABOUT
ALL I'VE GOT.
I HAVE MY TRUSTY
LAPTOP COMPUTER
AND A DIGITAL CAMERA.
OH, AND I'VE GOT
A SMALL CELL PHONE, TOO.
OF COURSE,
NOT ONE OF THEM'S WORKED
SINCE WE GOT HERE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DRAGGED
ALL THAT
COMPUTER STUFF
TO SUMMER CAMP.
AND WHAT DO YOU HAVE?
UH, LET'S SEE.
THERE'S MY
MINI-TELESCOPE.
SORRY, BUT I DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO EAT EITHER.
HEY,
LOOK AT WHAT I GOT.
CHECK IT OUT.
WOW, LOOK AT
ALL THOSE GOODIES!
WHY DON'T YOU BE
A GOOD LITTLE BOY
AND SHARE THOSE TREATS
WITH DEAR SWEET MIMI?
AWW, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BE SO NICE, MIMI.
I'M HAPPY TO SHARE.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
ISN'T SHE CUTE?
FORGET IT.
I'M SO HUNGRY
I COULD EAT A HORSE.
I'D SETTLE
FOR A SMALL COW.
MIMI, WHAT HAVE YOU
GOT IN THAT BIG BAG?
SOME HAIRBRUSHES
AND MAKEUP?
UH, WELL,
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
HERE'S A COMPASS,
COOKING FUEL, FLASHLIGHT,
ONE OF THOSE KNIVES
WITH ALL THE THINGS
AND SOME OTHER STUFF.
[ALL GASP]
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL US
YOU HAD A COMPASS
BACK WHEN
WE NEEDED ONE?
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE
KIND OF FUN TO SEE
HOW FAR WE COULD GET
WITHOUT ONE.
BESIDES, IT'S BROKEN.
WELL, SO MUCH
FOR FINDING OUR WAY
OUT OF HERE.
ALTHOUGH, WE COULD USE
THE COOKING FUEL
TO MAKE A SIGNAL FIRE.
THAT'S TRUE, OR I GUESS
WE CAN BARBECUE
SOME TELEPHONES.
OH, BOY,
CHECK OUT THE GENIUS.
SEE, HE'S TRYING
TO CALL THE TELEPHONE
REPAIR MAN
BECAUSE THE TELEPHONES
DON'T WORK.
PROBLEM IS--LOOK!
JOE'S GOT
THE EMERGENCY FOOD.
NO WAY.
Tai: JOE! HEY, JOE, LOOK,
YOU'VE GOT ALL THE FOOD.
HEY, DON'T YOU KNOW
IT'S RUDE TO
INTERRUPT SOMEONE
WHEN THEY'RE
ON THE TELEPHONE?
T.K.: BUT THAT BAG.
THIS? I JUST BROUGHT IT
TO GIVE TO MIMI.
TODAY WAS HER DAY
TO CARRY THE BAG.
THINK HE LIKES YOU.
NO WAY.
MIMI, YOU HAVE
GOT TO STOP
THINKING OF YOURSELF
AND DO SOMETHING
TO HELP SOMEBODY
ELSE FOR ONCE.
TAKE A LITTLE
RESPONSIBILITY.
BUT THAT BAG'S
TOO HEAVY FOR ME.
LISTEN, YOU NEVER
HEAR ME COMPLAINING.
GUYS, GUYS.
LISTEN, THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING NOW
IS THAT WE'VE GOT
SOME FOOD TO EAT.
SO LET'S SIT DOWN
AND HAVE SOME LUNCH.
UH-HUH.
[HUMMING]
Joe: OK,
LET'S FIGURE THIS OUT.
THERE'S 7 PEOPLE
IN THE GROUP
TIMES 3 DAYS.
TIMES 3 MEALS
THAT COMES TO...
63 MEALS.
UH, RIGHT. SO,
SPLIT EVENLY BETWEEN US
WE HAVE, UH...
ENOUGH FOOD
FOR 3 DAYS.
RIGHT, OH, UH, EXACTLY.
I GUESS YOU KNEW THAT.
Sora:
BUT, YOU GUYS, WHEN
YOU ADD IN THE DIGIMON
WE REALLY ONLY
HAVE ENOUGH FOR
ABOUT HALF AN HOUR.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
NOT A PROBLEM AT ALL.
WE DIGIMON HUNT
AND FORAGE FOR OURSELVES.
HUH?
YOU DO?
YOU DON'T NEED
TO INCLUDE US
IN YOUR CALCULATIONS.
YOU SURE, BIYOMON?
OH, ABSOLUTELY.
WE CAN DO ALL RIGHT
FOR OURSELVES.
OK, NOW THAT THAT'S
TAKEN CARE OF,
LET'S GO AHEAD
AND DIVIDE THIS BETWEEN
THE 7 PEOPLE HERE.
THIS IS GREAT. I COULD
EAT A DOZEN OF THESE.
JUST WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
I'M GLAD WE NEVER
HEAR YOU COMPLAINING.
MMM, YOU PEOPLE
MAKE ME CRAZY.
[HUMMING]
[GROWLING]
UH-OH.
HMM.
NOW WHAT'S
THE MATTER?
TROUBLE.
OH.
[BOTH GASP]
WHAT'S THAT?
SHELLMON.
WHAT'S A SHELLMON?
SOMETHING THAT GETS MAD
FOR NO REASON.
[ROARS]
Joe: ATTACKED BY
2 DIGITAL MONSTERS
IN THE SAME DAY.
AND DOESN'T SHELLMON KNOW
I'M ALLERGIC TO SHELLFISH?
EVERYBODY, UP HERE!
AAAH!
JOE!
DIGIMON ATTACK!
RIGHT.
[GROWLS]
AGUMON, YOU SHOW HIM!
PENTABREATH.
BLUE BLASTER.
SPIRAL TWISTER!
SUPER SHOCKER.
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO THEM?
THEY LOOK LIKE
THEY'VE LOST
THEIR POWERS.
AAAAH!
WHAAAAH!
AGUMON!
BLOW BOMB--AAAAH!
POISON IVY!
HUH?
AAAAH!
[DEEP BREATH]
GO GET HIM, AGUMON.
WHY IS IT ONLY AGUMON?
WE'RE JUST TOO HUNGRY.
WHAT?
GABUMON.
I DON'T HAVE
ANY STRENGTH.
THAT'S IT.
AGUMON IS THE ONLY ONE
WHO HAD ANYTHING TO EAT.
NOW I SEE.
THEN THE OTHER DIGIMON
DON'T HAVE ENOUGH STRENGTH
LEFT TO FIGHT.
AGUMON, LOOKS LIKE
ITS JUST YOU AND ME NOW.
THEN GIVE ME
A DIVERSION.
HEY, SHELLMON,
UGLY, OVER HERE!
NO, DON'T!
THIS'LL WORK.
HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT?
AAAH!
HOLD ON, TAI!
[ROAR]
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
All: WHOAAAH!
WATCH OUT!
HE'S GONNA
GET EVERYONE!
AND THERE'S
NOTHING I CAN DO!
AAAAAH!
TAI, NO!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
AAAAH! [GRUNTS]
DIGIVOLVE!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ALL GASP]
AGUMON,
DIGIVOLVE TO...
GREYMON!
AAAAAAH!
[LAUGHS]
WHOA, HE DID IT AGAIN.
NOW HE'S GREYMON.
[LAUGHING]
[GROWLS AND ROARS]
NOW YOU'RE GETTING HIM!
GO, GREYMON!
DIGINOVA BLAST!
[GASPS]
WHAT? AGUMON!
OH. ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU POOR LITTLE GUY,
AGUMON.
TAI? TAI!
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING TO EAT?
[LAUGHING]
Joe:
HELLO? COME ON,
I KNOW YOU'RE THERE.
OPERATOR, OPERATOR!
Tai: THERE'S
REALLY NO REASON
TO STAY HERE NOW.
Matt:
WHO WANTS TO BREAK
THE BAD NEWS TO JOE?
WHO WANTS SOME MORE?
JUST SAY SO.
SHELLMON
WASN'T DESTROYED.
HE WAS JUST
TEMPORARILY REMOVED.
WE SHOULD
PACK UP AND LEAVE
BEFORE HE DECIDES
HE WANTS TO COME BACK
FOR ROUND 2.
GOOD IDEA.
IN THAT CASE, WE SHOULD GO
RIGHT BACK TO THE FOREST,
BECAUSE IF ANYBODY'S
LOOKING FOR US, THAT'S
THE PLACE THEY'LL GO.
JOE,
I SAID THIS BEFORE,
WE FELL OFF A CLIFF
AND FLOATED DOWN A RIVER
TO GET HERE,
AND GETTING BACK THERE
IS A REALLY BIG JOB.
AND WE COULD RUN
INTO KUWAGAMON.
NOW, LISTEN,
LOGICALLY SPEAKING,
IF THERE ARE
TELEPHONES HERE,
THEN THERE MUST BE
PEOPLE TO USE THEM.
SO I THINK
IT MAKES GOOD SENSE
TO TRY AND
FIND THOSE PEOPLE.
THAT MAKES
SENSE?
IT CERTAINLY DOES.
THEN LET'S ALL
GET GOING.
ANYWHERE YOU WANT TO GO,
I'LL GO, TAI. YOU JUST
PICK THE DIRECTION.
THEN LET'S GET OUT
OF THIS PLACE.
AND LET
THE MONSTERS BEWARE.
MM-HMM.
WELL, MY PLAN IS
TO AVOID ALL MONSTERS.
YEP, THAT'S MY PLAN.
OK, HERE WE GO!
All: DIGIMON! [CHEERING]