Joe: MIMI AND I MADE OUR WAY
TO PRIMARY VILLAGE,
WHERE WE FOUND ELECMON,
WHO RESOLVED TO JOIN
OUR RAGTAG GROUP.
KNOWING MIMI WOULD BE SAFE,
I MADE
THE SAME DECISION AS MATT --
TO FIND WHAT KIND
OF PERSON I AM
AND MAKE SURE
I CAN BE COUNTED ON.
TAI AND HIS CREW MADE IT
TO THE TOP OF SPIRAL MOUNTAIN,
WHERE THEY CAME FACE TO FACE
WITH LADY DEVIMON.
SORA AND T.K.
SET OUT TO FIND US
FOR THE FINAL CONFRONTATION,
WHILE TAI AND IZZY STAYED
TO KEEP PIEDMON BUSY.
YOU THINK HE'D MIND
RESCHEDULING OUR DESTRUCTION?
GUESS NOT.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
WE'VE LOOKED
EVERYWHERE, GOMAMON,
WE STILL
CAN'T FIND MATT.
MAYBE YOUR HARMONICA PLAYING
IS KEEPING HIM IN HIDING.
Joe: EVERYBODY'S
A CRITIC.
HEY, JOE,
LOOK OVER THERE.
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S MATT'S BOAT.
HE MUST BE CLOSE BY.
Joe: BUT WE HAVE NO IDEA
OF WHEN HE LEFT IT
OR IF HE WAS
USING IT AT ALL.
DON'T BE SUCH A DOWNER.
THIS IS OUR FIRST CLUE
IN A LONG TIME,
AND I WANT TO SEE
A LITTLE GET-UP-AND-GOMAMON.
I'M PESSIMISTIC 'CAUSE WHEN
WE FOUND MATT'S HARMONICA,
IT LED US NOWHERE.
BUT YOU'RE RIGHT.
HE COULD BE NEARBY.
NOW THAT'S
THE SPIRIT, JOE.
YOU'VE BECOME
A REAL MAN LATELY.
OH, I GET IT NOW.
YOU'RE SAYING I WASN'T
A REAL MAN BEFORE, HUH?
ARE YOU MAN ENOUGH
NOT TO LAUGH
WHEN I TICKLE YOU?
MEGACLAW!
I THINK WE WON.
[ PIEDMON LAUGHS EVILLY ]
THANK YOU
FOR THE SPARRING MATCH,
WARGREYMON.
NOW I'M READY
FOR THE MAIN EVENT.
OH, NO!
ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WERE THESE DIGIDESTINED,
AND THEN PIEDMON
DESTROYED THEM ALL.
THE END.
NO OFFENSE
TO YOUR STORYTELLING,
BUT I'D LIKE IT BETTER
IF YOUR ENDING WERE DIFFERENT.
WE CAN'T WIN
UNLESS WE'RE ALL TOGETHER.
WHERE ARE THEY?
[ SCREECHES ]
THE DIGIVICE
ISN'T RESPONDING AT ALL.
I HOPE WE FIND THEM SOON.
I'M GETTING AIRSICK.
[ Thinking ] WE'LL NEVER
FIND THEM ALL.
THE DIGITAL WORLD IS TOO BIG.
THEY COULD BE ANYWHERE.
HEY, SORA?
WHAT?
WE'LL FIND MATT
AND THE OTHERS, RIGHT?
[ Thinking ] SHOULD I
TELL HIM THE TRUTH?
WELL, SORA?
THE ONLY THING
I CAN SAY, T.K., IS...
[ CRIES ]
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU'RE NOT CRYING, ARE YOU?
JUST SOMETHING IN MY EYE.
DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL FIND THEM, T.K.
[ SIGHS ]
[ Thinking ] WE'LL
FIND THE OTHERS
BECAUSE WE HAVE TO.
UNLESS WE FIGHT AS A TEAM,
WE'LL NEVER DEFEAT PIEDMON.
WE CAN'T LET HIM DESTROY
THE DIGITAL WORLD.
[ SCREECHES ]
TERRAFORCE!
[ GROWLS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
HE'S TOUGH.
Kari: WE SHOULD ALL FIGHT.
EVERYONE
STAY WHERE YOU ARE.
WHY NOT?
THE DIGIMON
ARE STILL TIRED
FROM OUR FIGHT
WITH LADY DEVIMON.
WE HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL WE'RE AT FULL STRENGTH
WHEN MATT AND THE OTHERS
REJOIN US.
Wargreymon:
I HOPE IT'S SOON.
MATT?
YEAH, GABUMON?
MAYBE WE'VE BEEN
TRAVELING IN THIS DIRECTION
A LITTLE TOO LONG.
THIS CAVE IS STARTING
TO GIVE ME THE CREEPS.
LET'S HURRY UP
AND GET OUT OF HERE.
I'M STILL NOT SURE
WHAT YOU MEAN
BY TRYING
TO FIND YOURSELF,
BUT I'D APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU DIDN'T LOOK HERE.
SURE. WHATEVER.
Joe: HEY.
SEE, EVERYBODY?
I TOLD YOU I'D BE BACK.
I CAN TAKE CARE
OF MYSELF JUST FINE.
[ MATT SIGHS ]
I'VE BEEN LIVING A LIE.
YOU'RE NOT A REAL BLOND?
[ SIGHS ]
I KEPT SAYING
T.K. NEEDED ME,
BUT REALLY I WAS THE ONE
WHO NEEDED HIM.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I USED TO THINK
THAT MY ONE PURPOSE IN LIFE
WAS TO PROTECT
MY LITTLE BROTHER,
BUT THEN...
YOU'RE THE MAN.
NICE GOING, T.K.
GREAT JOB, BUDDY.
WE WERE WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
BOY, FOR A LITTLE KID,
THAT WAS A PRETTY BIG ESCAPE.
HE DIDN'T NEED ME
TO PROTECT HIM ANYMORE,
AND TAI WAS MUCH BETTER
AT ACTING LIKE A BIG BROTHER
THAN I EVER WAS.
BUT YOU
DON'T HAVE TO ACT.
YOU ARE
T.K.'s BROTHER.
TAI ISN'T.
THAT'S
JUST THE POINT.
I DON'T ACT
LIKE A BROTHER AT ALL,
AND EVEN THOUGH
IT MADE ME FEEL GOOD
TO THINK THAT I WAS
THE ONLY ONE THERE FOR HIM,
IN REALITY
ALL THE KIDS WERE.
THERE'S SOMETHING STRANGE
ABOUT THIS PLACE.
THAT'S WHY TAI
MADE ME SO MAD.
I THOUGHT HE WAS TRYING
TO TAKE T.K. AWAY.
[ SIGHS ]
TAI MIGHT BE REAL BOSSY
AND HARDHEADED SOMETIMES,
BUT HE NEVER
TREATED T.K. LIKE A CHILD,
WHICH IS HOW
I'VE ALWAYS TREATED HIM,
BUT I'M THE ONE
WHO'S CHILDISH.
MATT, STOP PUTTING
YOURSELF DOWN.
SURE YOU HAVE
SOME TEENAGE ANGST,
BUT YOU'VE BEEN
A GREAT BROTHER TO T.K.
I USED TO THINK
TAI NEVER THOUGHT
ABOUT ANYONE BUT HIMSELF,
BUT THAT ACTUALLY
DESCRIBES ME A LOT BETTER.
[ SIGHS ]
OH, MATT.
OH, MATT!
I THINK YOU'D BETTER
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
WHATEVER.
I'M NO GOOD.
I CAN NEVER GO BACK
TO BEING THEIR FRIEND.
YOU HAVE TO.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND
THAT IF THE EIGHT OF YOU
DON'T GET BACK TOGETHER
THE DIGITAL WORLD
WILL BE DESTROYED FOREVER?
THEY DON'T NEED ME,
AND BESIDES,
SEVEN IS A LUCKIER NUMBER
THAN EIGHT.
HEY, MATT,
SNAP OUT OF IT.
JUST GO AWAY.
I WANT TO BE ALONE.
COME TO YOUR SENSES.
MATT, LISTEN...
OW! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU CRAZY?
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND, MATT?
YOU'VE GOT TO QUIT
COMPARING YOURSELF TO TAI.
YOU'RE NOT HIM.
IT'S LIKE ICE CREAM.
HE'S VANILLA,
YOU'RE ROCKY ROAD,
BUT ONLY ONE OF YOU
IS T.K.'s REAL BROTHER,
AND IT'S NOT HIM.
NO MATTER HOW MUCH
HE IMPRESSES T.K.,
TAI WILL NEVER BREAK THE BOND
THAT YOU TWO SHARE.
GABUMON.
AND BESIDES,
DON'T YOU THINK
IT WOULD BREAK MY HEART
IF YOU WEREN'T HERE?
AFTER ALL, I DIDN'T WAIT
MY ENTIRE LIFE
FOR YOU TO ARRIVE
JUST SO YOU COULD
WALLOW IN SELF-PITY,
BUT, MATT, IF YOU REALLY
WANT TO BE LEFT ALONE
THEN I'LL RESPECT YOUR WISHES
AND DISAPPEAR,
BUT ONLY IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU REALLY WANT ME TO DO.
NO, I DON'T REALLY
WANT TO BE LEFT ALONE.
SORRY. I NEVER
MEANT TO HURT YOU.
AW.
I'VE NEVER LET ANYONE
GET CLOSE TO ME BEFORE,
NOT SINCE
MY FAMILY SPLIT UP.
EVER SINCE THEN
I'VE BEEN ALONE.
I FIGURED IF MY FAMILY
DIDN'T WANT ME,
THEN I WOULD JUST
KEEP TO MYSELF
AND NEVER TELL ANYONE
WHAT I WAS FEELING,
AND I SWORE I WOULD NEVER
LET ANYONE SEE ME CRY.
BUT REALLY ALL I WANTED
TO DO WAS CRY.
THEN CRY.
[ Crying ] I HATE
BEING ALONE.
I'M HERE FOR YOU, MATT.
I USED TO BE LONELY, TOO.
I WANDERED AROUND
THE DIGITAL WORLD
WITHOUT ANY FRIENDS AT ALL.
AFTER I MET YOU, I KNEW
I'D NEVER BE LONELY AGAIN.
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
ME TOO.
YOU'RE THE REASON I CAME
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
IN THE FIRST PLACE,
AND HERE I AM,
LOST IN THIS DARK
STRANGE CAVE,
AND YOU'RE STILL
RIGHT BY MY SIDE.
THAT'S THE SIGN
OF A TRUE FRIEND.
I GUESS
I HAVE FRIENDS,
AND THAT INCLUDES T.K.
AND MY MOM AND DAD.
[ Thinking ] NOW I REALIZE
I WAS NEVER REALLY ALONE.
PEOPLE LIKE ME.
THEY REALLY,
REALLY LIKE ME.
Gabumon: MATT, LOOK.
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S BEEN AROUND YOU
THIS WHOLE TIME.
YOU MEAN YOU HAVEN'T
NOTICED IT UNTIL NOW?
NOT AT ALL.
IT WAS WEIRD.
THE MORE YOU TALKED
ABOUT BEING ALONE,
THE BIGGER
THAT THING GOT.
IT'S PITCH BLACK.
THAT'S EXACTLY THE FEELING
I HAD IN MY HEART
JUST A MINUTE AGO.
I KNOW WHAT IT IS.
PLEASE, TELL ME.
IT'S THE DARKNESS
THAT I'VE BEEN
CARRYING AROUND WITH ME
THIS WHOLE TIME,
THE DARKNESS THAT'S
BEEN BURIED IN MY HEART.
OH, GABUMON,
NOW IT'S READY
TO SWALLOW ME UP WHOLE.
LIKE JONAH
AND THE WHALE?
IF I DIDN'T
RECOGNIZE IT JUST NOW,
IT WOULD HAVE TAKEN OVER
MY WHOLE LIFE,
BUT I'M NOT GOING
TO LET THAT HAPPEN.
IT CAN'T HURT ME
BECAUSE I'M NOT ALONE
ANYMORE.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
I WANT
TO THANK YOU, GABUMON.
DON'T MENTION IT. THAT'S
WHAT FRIENDS ARE FOR.
BESIDES, I SHOULD
BE THANKING YOU.
YOU'RE THE BEST FRIEND
A DIGIMON EVER HAD.
LET'S PROMISE WE'LL ALWAYS
BE THERE FOR EACH OTHER,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
GABUMON AND MATT,
FRIENDS FOR LIFE.
MM.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
DO WE HAVE A DEAL?
A HANDSHAKE
MAKES IT OFFICIAL.
WILL A PAW-SHAKE DO?
AND I PROMISE NOT
TO COMPLAIN ANYMORE, EITHER.
DON'T START THAT AGAIN.
IF YOU'RE UPSET
ABOUT SOMETHING,
YOU SHOULD GET IT
OFF YOUR CHEST.
ALL RIGHT,
IF YOU INSIST.
I'LL STILL COMPLAIN
ONCE IN A WHILE,
BUT ONLY TO YOU.
[ LAUGHS ]
CORRECT ME IF I'M WRONG
ON THIS ONE, MATT,
BUT WEREN'T WE
IN A BIG DARK CAVE
A MINUTE AGO?
THAT'S RIGHT, AND WE
WERE COMPLETELY LOST.
Joe: HEY, MATT.
OVER HERE.
IT'S JOE.
[ PANTING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
HMM?
WHO'S THE MAN NOW?
TOLD YOU I'D FIND HIM.
I NEVER DOUBTED YOU
FOR A SINGLE MINUTE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I SAID TO MYSELF, "JOE,
JUST FOLLOW YOUR OWN PATH,
AND SOONER OR LATER
YOU'LL RUN INTO MATT."
I'M JUST GLAD IT HAPPENED
BEFORE I RETIRED.
I SEE.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I FORGOT. HERE.
IT'S YOUR HARMONICA,
ISN'T IT?
THANKS, JOE.
MM-HMM.
TRUMP SWORDS.
AAH!
WARGREYMON'S EXHAUSTED.
I CAN'T WATCH ANYMORE.
STAY TOUGH.
[ PANTING ]
PLEASE, IZZY,
LET ME HELP WARGREYMON.
Tai: NO.
WARGREYMON NEEDS HELP.
[ Thinking ] COME ON, MATT.
WHERE ARE YOU?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ SCREECHES ]
LOOK DOWN THERE.
THAT'S MATT'S BOAT.
BUT WHERE'S MATT?
I HOPE HE'S
NOT HURT SOMEWHERE.
WE'LL NEVER FIND HIM.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
[ Thinking ] T.K.'s RIGHT.
MAYBE WE SHOULD GO
AND HELP THE OTHERS FIGHT.
NO, TAI ASKED ME
TO FIND THE OTHERS,
AND THAT'S WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO.
I WON'T LET HIM DOWN.
SORA, WATCH OUT.
THERE'S SOME BLACK THING
COMING OUT OF THE GROUND.
HUH? AAH!
SORA! SORA!
T.K.
HEY, THAT SOUNDS
LIKE MATT.
IT SURE DOES.
MATT, WHERE HAVE
YOU BEEN?
I WAS SO WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
SORRY. I NEEDED TO GET
MY HEAD STRAIGHT,
BUT I WON'T
LEAVE YOU AGAIN.
I PROMISE YOU.
GEE, MATT,
YOU LOOK DIFFERENT.
DID YOU CUT YOUR HAIR
OR SOMETHING?
NO, I JUST HAVEN'T BEEN
USING AS MUCH GEL.
WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
SOME BLACK THING
PULLED SORA DOWN
INTO THAT HOLE.
WHAT?
IS SHE ALL RIGHT?
HEY, MATT, DOES THIS
REMIND YOU OF ANYTHING?
Matt: YEAH, IT LOOKS
JUST LIKE THAT CAVE
WE WERE
TRAPPED IN BEFORE.
THE SAME BLACK THING
MUST HAVE GOTTEN SORA.
YOU'VE SEEN IT?
WE'VE GOT TO HELP HER.
I DON'T HAVE
A GOOD FEELING ABOUT THIS.
T.K.: IT'S SCARY.
Matt: WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T BE AFRAID. OKAY, GUYS?
I'VE REALIZED
THAT IT'S YOUR FEAR
THAT FEEDS THE DARKNESS.
T.K.: THAT'S EASY
FOR YOU TO SAY.
WHOA. OH.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, JOE?
YEAH, FORTUNATELY I LANDED
ON THE ONE PART OF MY BODY
THAT HAS
A BUILT-IN AIR BAG.
VERY FUNNY.
WHERE'S SORA?
WE NEED A CLUE.
Patamon: LISTEN.
I THINK I HEAR SOMETHING
COMING FROM OVER THERE.
I'D CALL THAT A CLUE.
Biyomon: SORA.
SORA, TALK TO ME.
PLEASE TELL ME WHAT'S WRONG.
THAT'S BIYOMON'S VOICE.
WHICH MEANS SORA
CAN'T BE FAR BEHIND.
Biyomon: SORA. SORA.
HANG ON, BIYOMON.
WE'RE COMING.
OVER HERE.
SORA, WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU? GET UP.
[ STRUGGLES ]
SHE'S STUCK.
LET ME HELP.
ON 3. 1...2...3.
[ BOYS STRUGGLING ]
ONCE IT TOOK FOUR OF US
TO GET MY GRANDMOTHER
OFF THE TOILET LIKE THAT.
HEY, LISTEN.
SORA'S SAYING SOMETHING.
HUH?
I HAVE TO FIND MIMI
AND JOE AND MATT.
I HAVE TO HELP TAI,
OR THE WORLD WILL BE DESTROYED.
THERE'S NO PLACE LIKE HOME.
SHE WON'T TALK TO ME
ANYMORE.
ALL SHE DOES
IS KEEP MUMBLING
THE SAME THING
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
SORA, MATT AND I
ARE RIGHT HERE.
LOOK AT ME. FOCUS.
JOE, YOU'RE REALLY HERE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
AND MATT'S
WITH YOU, TOO.
JUST RELAX. EVERYTHING'S
GOING TO BE OKAY NOW.
I'M AFRAID NOT.
I HAVEN'T BEEN
TRYING HARD ENOUGH.
I HAVE TO GET TO TAI
AND HELP HIM FIGHT,
BECAUSE IF I DON'T,
THE WORLD WILL BE DESTROYED.
SORA, COME ON.
YOU CAN'T BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR SAVING THE WORLD.
REALIZE HOW STRONG
YOUR NEGATIVE FEELINGS ARE.
THEY PRODUCE
A DESTRUCTIVE ENERGY.
SORA, IT'S THE DARKNESS
IN YOUR HEART
THAT CREATED THE CAVE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
IS THAT WHY YOU TOLD T.K.
NOT TO BE SCARED?
Matt: SORA, LISTEN TO ME.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO MAKE THIS CAVE DISAPPEAR.
YOU'VE GOT TO REACH
DEEP INTO YOUR HEART
AND ERASE ALL
THE NEGATIVE FEELINGS.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
YOU'LL HAVE TO FIND
THE ANSWER TO THAT QUESTION
ON YOUR OWN.
SORA, THIS ISN'T
THE KIND OF THING
YOU DO JUST BECAUSE
YOU HAVE TO.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO, IT HAS
TO BE BECAUSE YOU WANT TO.
I DON'T HAVE TO DO IT
IF I DON'T WANT TO?
RIGHT. IT'LL ONLY WORK
IF YOU WANT TO DO IT.
I'M CONFUSED.
HOW WILL I KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO DO?
WHEN THIS
WHOLE THING STARTED,
DO YOU THINK
WE HAD ANY IDEA
WHAT THE RIGHT THING
TO DO WAS?
OF COURSE NOT, BUT THAT
DIDN'T STOP US, DID IT?
MAYBE WE'RE HERE
FOR A REASON,
MAYBE WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO CAN DO IT.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
IT'S WORKING, MATT.
I THINK WE'RE FINALLY
GETTING THROUGH TO HER.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE HERE.
HUH?
I GET IT NOW.
YOU WERE RIGHT, MATT.
HOW DID YOU KNOW?
I WENT THROUGH
THE SAME THING MYSELF.
WELCOME BACK.
[ GIGGLES ]
SORA.
BIYOMON.
I'M SO HAPPY
THAT YOU'RE THE OLD SORA,
NOT THE NEW SORA.
Joe: THE CAVE'S GONE.
Matt: WHEN THE DARKNESS
FROM SORA'S HEART DISAPPEARED,
SO DID THE CAVE.
I FEEL SO RELIEVED.
T.K.: BOY, WAIT TILL TAI
HEARS ABOUT THIS.
LET'S FIND HIM.
TAI'S WAITING FOR US
RIGHT NOW.
LET'S GO.
RIGHT.
TRUMP SWORDS.
UGH.
AAH!
GET UP, TAI!
HEY, TAI.
IZZY, STOP.
YOU STAY THERE.
PROTECT KARI.
AAH!
[ GROANS ]
TAI, LOOK, I KNOW
IT'S IMPORTANT FOR ME
TO STAY AND PROTECT KARI.
IN THE MEANTIME,
WHO'S GOING TO PROTECT YOU?
HE TENDS TO BE STUBBORN,
DOESN'T HE?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'M FINE.
I'VE GOT HIM
RIGHT WHERE I WANT HIM.
HE'S EXHAUSTED.
BUT I CAN HELP YOU.
I'M FINE.
THAT'S FUNNY.
GENERAL CUSTER
SAID THE EXACT SAME THING
AT LITTLE BIG HORN.
THANKS FOR
THE HISTORY LESSON.
ALL RIGHT THEN,
JUST ONE THING --
HOW COME
EVERY TIME I ASK,
YOU NEVER LET ME
JOIN IN THE FIGHT?
CLOWN TRICK.
AAH!
WARGREYMON'S BEEN HIT.
NO! WARGREYMON!
GET UP!
RIGHT. NOW, WHO
SHALL BE NEXT?
WARGREYMON, I'M COMING.
Matt: TAI, WHERE ARE YOU?
MATT.
HOLD ON, BUDDY.
WE'RE COMING.
Sora: TAI, IT'S US.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
ONCE UPON A TIME,
THEY WERE DIGIDESTINED.
NOW THEY'RE
JUST SITTING DUCKS
WAITING FOR ME
TO TAKE TARGET PRACTICE.
TAI.
MATT, YOU MADE IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE HERE.
YEAH, I MADE IT, TAI.
HANG IN THERE, BUDDY.
I NEVER DOUBTED YOU
FOR A SECOND, MATT.
I KNOW IT DIDN'T
ALWAYS SEEM THAT WAY.
THANK YOU, TAI,
FOR BELIEVE IN ME.
I'M JUST SORRY
I WAS SO LATE.
TAI, YOU HAVE TO KNOW
HOW MUCH OUR FRIENDSHIP
HAS ALWAYS MEANT TO ME,
AND I SWEAR
NOTHING WILL EVER
COME BETWEEN US AGAIN.
Matt: WARGREYMON.
NOW WHAT?
MATT, YOUR CREST
OF FRIENDSHIP
GAVE ME STRENGTH
AND BROUGHT WARGREYMON
BACK TO NORMAL.
THANK YOU, GARURUMON.
NOW I CAN FIGHT AGAIN.
Izzy: COME ON, GUYS.
GET OUT OF THERE.
Joe: TAI, ARE YOU OKAY?
Tai: I THINK SO.
MY FIRST THOUGHT
WAS TO DESTROY YOU
ALL TOGETHER IN ONE
NICE LITTLE PACKAGE,
BUT NOW I BELIEVE
I'D RATHER DO IT INDIVIDUALLY
SO AS TO PROLONG YOUR SUFFERING
A LITTLE LONGER.
YOU SURE TALK A LOT
FOR A CLOWN.
TRUMP SWORD.
GABUMON,
WARP DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ WARP DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
METAL GARURUMON.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
NOW HE'LL SEE
WHAT WE'RE MADE OF.
♪ HEY, DIGIMON,
HEY, DIGIMON ♪
♪ MONSTER FRIENDS
TO THE BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
THEY WERE ABLE TO BREAK
PIEDMON'S ATTACK. ALL RIGHT.
WELL, COULD IT
ACTUALLY BE THE CASE
THAT I'VE FINALLY
FOUND AN ADVERSARY
WORTH FIGHTING?
♪ CHAMPIONS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
WILL WARGREYMON
AND METAL GARURUMON
HAVE ENOUGH STRENGTH
TO DEFEAT PIEDMON,
THE LAST OF THE DARK MASTERS?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."