Tai: DATAMON KNEW SORA
WOULDN'T HELP HIM FIGHT ETEMON,
SO HE CREATED
AN EXACT DOUBLE OF HER.
WE STAGED A GREAT PLAN
TO BREAK INTO THE PYRAMID
AND RESCUE HER,
A PLAN SO GOOD
IT ACTUALLY WORKED.
DATAMON OPENED A HOLE
TO THE CENTER
OF THE POWER NETWORK
AND WAS SUCKED IN
ALONG WITH ETEMON
AND EVERYTHING ELSE.
ETEMON SOON RETURNED
FOR A BIG SHOWDOWN.
USING THE POWER
OF MY TAG AND CREST,
GREYMON DIGIVAULTED
TO METAL GREYMON
AND DEFEATED HIM.
UNFORTUNATELY,
WE WERE CAUGHT IN THE VORTEX.
THERE'S NO TELLING WHAT
STRANGE WORLD WE'LL LAND IN.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Tai: WHEN WE DEFEATED ETEMON,
SOMETHING VERY STRANGE
HAPPENED.
NO WAY!
WHAT HAPPENED?
WE MUST HAVE BEEN PULLED
THROUGH SOME SORT
OF DIMENSIONAL OPENING
BETWEEN DIGIWORLD AND THIS ONE,
WHEREVER THIS ONE IS.
I BET THAT OPENING'S THE WAY
I GOT TO DIGIWORLD,
BUT WHERE ARE WE NOW?
THEY LOOK LIKE HUMAN BEINGS.
THIS LOOKS LIKE EARTH,
BUT IS IT REALLY?
I DON'T KNOW. I'VE NEVER
BEEN HERE BEFORE.
THIS CAN'T BE.
THIS LOOKS LIKE A PARK
I PLAYED IN AS A KID.
WE'RE IN MY HOMETOWN.
Koromon: NO WAY!
YEAH, THAT'S THE TOY FACTORY,
AND THAT'S CITY HALL
OVER THERE.
I DON'T MEAN TO CUT
THE SIGHTSEEING TOUR SHORT,
BUT HAVE YOU NOTICED
I'M NOT METAL GREYMON ANYMORE?
I'M BACK TO KOROMON.
UNBELIEVABLE.
THIS CAN'T BE REAL.
IT FEELS REAL TO --
OHH!
HUH? HEY!
TELL ME, WHERE ARE WE?
IS THIS WORLD FOR REAL,
OR AM I IMAGINING IT?
WHAT?
WE WANT TO KNOW
IF YOU'RE REAL.
PLEASE TELL US.
ARE YOU A REAL GIRL
OR A DIGITAL GIRL?
WAAH!
WHAT DID I DO?
DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
YOU SCARED HER. SHE'S GOING
TO TELL THE PARK POLICE.
THE POLICE?
WILL THEY ARREST ME
FOR MAKING HER CRY?
SAVE ME, TAI.
THEY'RE GOING TO GET ME.
BE QUIET. LISTEN UP.
PRETEND YOU'RE A SOCCER BALL.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE
SO I CAN CHILL AND FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON.
THIS ALL LOOKS SO FAMILIAR.
THIS HAS TO BE MY HOME.
WELL, FOR YOUR SAKE,
I HOPE SO.
HOW CAN YOU BE CERTAIN
YOU'RE NOT IMAGINING IT
IN THE DIGIWORLD, TAI?
WE'LL FIND OUT WHEN WE GO
TO MY HOUSE AND SEE.
DID YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID?
"UNTIL WE GO TO MY HOUSE."
WOW! THIS HAS GOT TO BE
THE HAPPIEST DAY OF MY LIFE.
I'M HOME, I'M HOME, I'M HOME!
IT'S TRUE, I'M HOME.
THIS IS SO COOL.
I'M FINALLY HOME!
I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE MY FAMILY.
WHEN THEY LOOK AT YOU,
THEY'LL KNOW
I'M TELLING THE TRUTH.
THEN WE'LL SEE
IF THE OTHERS GOT HOME
AND HOOK UP WITH THEM.
MM, I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
IT'S A GOOD THING
I STILL HAD SOME
OF MY CAMP MONEY LEFT.
THE SUBWAY'S A LOT NICER
THAN WALKING HOME.
WOW! EVERYTHING LOOKS
EXACTLY THE WAY IT DID
ON THE DAY I LEFT FOR CAMP.
Boy: COME ON!
THAT'S WHERE I LIVE.
PRETTY NEAT, DON'T YOU THINK?
ALL THOSE ROOMS?
YOUR FAMILY'S BIG.
IT'S AN APARTMENT BUILDING.
LOTS OF FAMILIES LIVE THERE.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO EXPECT.
EVERYTHING'S BEEN SO WEIRD.
BEING IN DIGIWORLD,
I'VE LOST TRACK OF TIME.
I WONDER IF THEY'RE EVEN
GOING TO RECOGNIZE ME.
Koromon: WE WON'T KNOW
UNLESS WE GO IN.
RIGHT. WELL, HERE GOES.
IT'S UNLOCKED.
THEY MUST BE HOME.
I REMEMBER WHEN MY MOM
PLANTED THOSE FLOWERS.
I REMEMBER BUZZING
MY FRIENDS UP ON THAT INTERCOM
TO COME OVER AND PLAY
VIDEO GAMES AND WATCH TV,
OH, AND THE TIME WHEN MY DAD
PUT OUR FAMILY NAMEPLATE
ON THIS DOOR,
BUT THOSE MEMORIES
WON'T MEAN A THING, KOROMON,
IF WE CAME OUT
OF THAT DIMENSION RIFT
AT THE WRONG TIME.
WHAT IF I NO LONGER EXIST?
CAN I MAKE A SUGGESTION?
HUH?
OPEN THE DOOR.
HERE WE GO.
HELLO? LOOK.
THEIR SHOES ARE HERE.
MOM? DAD?
NO ONE'S ANSWERING.
MAYBE THEY'RE OUT.
I WONDER
WHERE THEY'VE GONE.
MAYBE THEY WENT
TO DIGIWORLD.
THAT'S NOT FUNNY!
HEY, TAI, OVER HERE.
I'M THIRSTY.
SORRY,
IT'S THE LAST ONE.
YOU SHOULD HAVE ASKED
BEFORE I STARTED DRINKING IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'D BE SO STINGY!
I WAS JUST JOKING,
CRYBABY.
REALLY?
I LEFT YOU HALF OF IT.
I SURE WISH I KNEW
WHERE MY FAMILY WAS
AND HOW LONG
I'VE BEEN GONE.
HUH? AHA!
DON'T SCARE ME
LIKE THAT!
IT'S BEEN RIGHT
IN FRONT OF ME.
TODAY'S AUGUST 1st --
THE DAY WE LANDED IN DIGIWORLD.
WE'VE GONE BACK
IN TIME?
THIS IS THE DAY THE DIGIVICES
DROPPED INTO OUR HANDS
AND THIS CRAZY ADVENTURE BEGAN.
THIS IS ALSO THE DAY
MOM AND DAD WERE PLANNING
TO VISIT MY GRANDMOTHER,
WHO LIVES OUTSIDE THE CITY.
SEE, MY MOM MARKED THE DATE
ON THIS CALENDAR
SO SHE WOULDN'T FORGET.
THEY MUST HAVE TAKEN
MY SISTER KARI WITH THEM.
THAT'S WHY NOBODY'S HOME NOW.
COOL!
LET'S JUST KICK BACK AND WAIT
FOR THEM TO COME HOME.
SPEAKING OF TIME,
IT'S TIME TO EAT.
HOLD YOUR DIGIHORSES.
I'VE JUST LEARNED I'M RELIVING
A DAY I'VE ALREADY LIVED.
SORRY, TAI.
NO, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO YELL,
BUT THIS SAME HOUR,
MINUTE, AND SECOND
HAVE ALREADY OCCURRED,
EXCEPT I'M HOME THIS TIME.
DOES THAT MEAN I HAVE A TWIN
LIVING IN SOME PARALLEL WORLD?
[ YAWNING ]
WHAT WAS THAT?
HEAR THAT?
HI, TAI.
KARI, YOU'RE HERE?
MOM AND DAD LEFT YOU
HERE AT HOME ALL ALONE?
I'M A BIG GIRL.
HI, KOROMON.
KARI, HOW DID
YOU KNOW HIS NAME?
MAYBE SHE KNOWS MY NAME
BECAUSE YOUR SISTER'S
SMARTER THAN YOU.
CUT IT OUT, KOROMON!
HOW DID YOU KNOW
HIS NAME WAS KOROMON?
I JUST KNEW IT.
I DON'T GET IT.
IT'S LIKE I'VE MET HIM.
THAT'S WHY I'M NOT AFRAID.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
HE'S BEEN OUT OF DIGIWORLD.
WELL, MAYBE
THAT'S WHERE WE MET.
BUT YOU'VE NEVER BEEN
TO DIGIWORLD, HAVE YOU?
I DON'T KNOW. I THINK SO.
IT'S NEAR YOU CAMP.
MAYBE KARI
HAS BEEN TO DIGIWORLD.
SHE DID HAVE ON
THAT CAMP WHISTLE.
MAYBE SHE GOES TO MY CAMP
IN THE FUTURE
AND IS SUCKED INTO DIGIWORLD
LIKE I WAS
BUT COMES BACK BEFORE ME.
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
THIS MOVING BACK AND FORTH
FROM ONE TIME DIMENSION
TO ANOTHER IS MEGA-WHACKED.
NO ONE'S EVER SURE
WHETHER THEY'RE HERE AND NOW
OR THERE AND THEN.
SOMETIMES I FEEL MORE
LIKE I'M WHERE AND WHEN,
RATHER THAN HERE OR THERE OR --
WHAT DID I JUST SAY?
I'M CONFUSING MYSELF.
I KNOW.
MAYBE KARI AND I HAVE A FEVER,
AND WE'RE BOTH DELIRIOUS.
WHAT'S WRONG, TAI?
NOTHING.
WHY DO YOU THINK
I HAVE A FEVER?
I'M NOT SICK,
AND I'VE BEEN TO DIGIWORLD.
NO WAY.
WELL, I THINK YOU HAVE.
WHERE ELSE
COULD YOU FIND A KOROMON?
THE TOY STORE?
OH, PLEASE.
YOU DO KNOW.
I'D BETTER CALL
EVERYONE ELSE'S HOUSE
TO SEE
IF THEY GOT HOME, TOO.
Man: Hello?
HI. IS IZZY THERE, PLEASE?
SUMMER CAMP? OH.
THIS IS TAI.
I CAME HOME
FROM, UH, CAMP EARLY.
I JUST WANTED TO SEE
IF IZZY DID, TOO.
NO, EVERYTHING'S JUST FINE.
THANKS.
YOU HAVEN'T HEARD FROM SORA
SINCE SHE LEFT
FOR SUMMER CAMP?
MATT HASN'T CALLED HOME
OR ANYTHING?
OKAY, THANK YOU.
IT LOOKS LIKE
I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO GOT PULLED THROUGH
THAT RIFT.
EVERYBODY ELSE
IS STILL STUCK IN DIGIWORLD.
I WISH IZZY WERE HERE.
HE COULD GET THIS DIGIVICE
TO WORK.
I COULD GO BACK TO DIGIWORLD
AND RESCUE THE OTHERS.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A WAY TO FIX
THIS TIME DIMENSION THING.
Kari: TAI.
HUH?
THERE'S FOOD IN THE FRIDGE.
YOU CAN HAVE
MY LEFTOVER PIECE OF PIE.
I GET FIRST DIBS!
I'VE GOT A BETTER IDEA.
I'LL MAKE US
A HEALTHY BREAKFAST.
Tai: COME AND GET IT!
Kari and Tai:
IT'S GOOD TO BE HOME.
DELISH.
YOU SAID IT!
TAI, YOU'VE NEVER COOKED.
DID YOU LEARN IN CAMP?
MMM, YEAH.
MY NEW FRIEND MATT TAUGHT ME
WHEN OUR SUMMER CAMP
SWITCHED TO DIGIWORLD.
YOU'RE GOOD.
I'M STUFFED.
YOU GUYS CAN EAT THE REST.
Koromon: GLAD TO!
WHOA!
I AM SO FULL
I WON'T HAVE TO EAT
FOR AT LEAST A YEAR.
OH, BOY!
HEY!
WHAT'S WRONG?
SO FULL. WAAH!
I'D BETTER GO REST.
Kari: DON'T HIDE
IN THE BATHROOM.
HOW EMBARRASSING.
WHY DO YOU WANT TO HANG OUT
WITH SUCH A PIG?
'CAUSE YOU'RE CUTE.
REALLY?
WANT TO HEAR
WHAT HAPPENED AT SCHOOL?
WE TOOK A FIELD TRIP,
AND I FELL IN A PIGPEN.
THE KIDS WERE LAUGHING
TILL TAI JUMPED IN.
HE PLAYED
IN THE MUD WITH ME,
LIKE I'D DONE IT
ON PURPOSE.
WOW!
TAI DOES BUG ME
SOMETIMES,
BUT HE IS THE COOLEST
BIG BROTHER.
MM, MM, AHH.
I'M REALLY BACK.
OH, I USED TO HATE
THAT WIND CHIME.
NOW I LOVE IT.
I REALLY MISS SITTING AROUND
WATCHIG TV WITH MY FRIENDS.
I MISS MOM SCOLDING DAD
FOR NOT HANGING UP HIS SHIRTS.
[ Yawns ]
BOY, IT'S GOOD TO BE HOME.
Man: UNBELIEVABLE WEATHER
CONDITIONS AROUND THE WORLD
HAVE WEATHER EXPERTS PUZZLED.
THERE IS STILL NO RAINFALL
IN SOUTHEAST ASIA,
AND ALL THE RICE PADDIES
ARE DRYING UP
AS A RESULT OF DROUGHT.
HMM, MERAMON.
AND THERE'S SEADRAMON.
IN THE MIDDLE EAST, FLOODING
CONTINUES TO WREAK HAVOC.
IN AMERICA, SNOW FALLS
IN A MIDSUMMER COLD SPELL.
WHAT? WHAT IS FRIGIMON
DOING HERE?
COULD SOMEBODY PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
THE DIGIMON ARE CLEARLY
ON THE TV SCREEN,
BUT THE REPORTER
HASN'T MENTIONED THEM.
FINALLY, SOMEBODY ELSE
CAN SEE THEM.
HUH? ARE YOU SAYING YOU CAN
SEE THE MONSTERS, TOO?
FOR A LONG TIME NOW.
MOM AND DAD JUST THINK
I WATCH TOO MANY SCARY MOVIES.
KARI.
UH-OH.
HUH?
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
MY DIGIVICE
HAS ACTIVATED ITSELF.
HUH?
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH THE COMPUTER, TAI?
THERE'S A FACE.
WHAT?
Can you hear me?
We -- danger.
IZZY?
They know it isn't --
Tai, wherever you may be,
don't come back here.
I CAN'T JUST LEAVE
YOU GUYS THERE, IZZY.
I HAVE TO COME BACK.
I COULD BE YOUR ONLY CHANCE.
Digimonsters --
total chaos.
WAIT. IZZY, I NEED HELP
WITH THE DIGIVICE.
You're better off where
you are. Don't come back.
IZZY! IZZY!
WHILE WE'RE HERE
SAFE AT HOME,
MY FRIENDS
ARE IN TROUBLE.
WHAT NOW?
I DON'T KNOW, KOROMON.
I JUST DON'T KNOW.
TWO WORLDS
ARE IN DANGER,
AND I CAN'T DO
A THING ABOUT IT.
I FEEL TOTALLY USELESS.
I KNOW THIS DIGIVICE
IS POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO DO SOMETHING,
BUT I DON'T HAVE A CLUE
ON HOW TO MAKE IT WORK.
OH, MAN, I GUESS I SHOULD
JUST QUIT WHILE I'M AHEAD.
BUT, TAI, YOU CAN'T.
WHY CAN'T I?
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO,
THROW THE DIGIVICE
AT THE MONSTERS
AND HOPE THEY GET SCARED
AND RUN AWAY?
COME ON, TAI.
JUST RELAX.
EAT SOME WATERMELON.
KARI'S RIGHT. I DO NEED
TO RELAX AND CHILL OUT.
MAYBE AN IDEA OF WHAT TO DO
WILL COME TO ME, I HOPE.
MMM, MMM, MMM.
BOY, OH, BOY,
IF THERE'S ONE THING I LOVE,
I LOVE THIS WATERMELON.
IT'S SWEET, HUH?
YOU CAN EAT
ALL YOU WANT, KOROMON.
WOW. I NEED
ANOTHER SLICE.
THIS WORLD IS GREAT.
MMM, MMM.
I'M GLAD YOU LIKE IT
HERE ON EARTH,
BECAUSE YOU MAY BE
STAYING HERE FOR A WHILE.
HUH?
YOU MAY NOT BE RETURNING
TO DIGIWORLD
ANY TIME SOON, IF AT ALL,
BUT YOU ARE MORE THAN WELCOME
TO LIVE WITH US FOREVER.
I DIDN'T HIT ME
UNTIL JUST NOW.
I MAY NEVER GET BACK
TO MY HOME.
[ SNORING ]
[ GROANING ]
TELEPHONE!
WHO IS IT?
MM-HMM.
I'LL SEE YOU, MOM.
LET ME HEAR.
We might be a little later
than planned.
There's supposed
to be a storm coming in,
and there might
be some heavy traffic
coming back into town.
Oh, your grandparents
want you and Tai
to come visit
when you get well.
Kari, are you listening?
Kari, are you
still there, honey?
MOM?
What? Tai?
UH...
WHAT'S HAPPENING, TAI?
NOW I UNDERSTAND.
EARTH IS IN AS MUCH DANGER
AS THE DIGIWORLD.
HOW?
DIGIWORLD'S TROUBLES
ARE SLIPPING
THROUGH THE DIMENSION.
WHAT CAN WE DO?
NOTHING, UNTIL I FIGURE OUT
HOW TO USE THE DIGIVICE
SO WE CAN RETURN TO DIGIWORLD
AND FIGHT THE BAD DIGIMON.
WE'LL BE OKAY FOR NOW.
THIS WILL BE A NICE BREAK.
HERE WE HAVE FOOD
AND CANDY AND STUFF,
AND WE SLEEP
IN A SOFT BED.
WE'LL BE LIVING LARGE.
RIGHT.
SORRY, DIGIBUD.
THERE'S LOTS OF THINGS TO DO.
THAT SATELLITE DISH
IS MORE IN TOUCH
WITH THE WORLD THAN WE ARE.
WE COULD GO TO THE BEACH,
THE MOVIES.
[ Sobbing ] YEAH.
WHAT AM I TALKING ABOUT?
MY FRIENDS ARE IN DANGER.
I CAN'T MAKE
THIS PIECE OF JUNK WORK,
AND I CAN'T DO A THING
ABOUT IT! UGH!
WHAT'S THAT?
EARTHQUAKE!
WHAT? IS IT SEADRAMON AGAIN?
OH, NO! TYRANOMON!
WHAT'S HE GOING TO DO?
[ GROWLING ]
NO.
WHAT ABOUT ME AND KARI?
SHE STAYS HERE.
KARI, DON'T LEAVE
FOR ANY REASON.
KOROMON AND I HAVE TO FIND
THAT DIMENSIONAL RIFT.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO DIGIWORLD.
NO. OH...
[ PANTING ]
Both: HUH?
WHAT -- WHAT HAPPENED?
HE'S GONE.
HUH?
[ GROWLING ]
DORIMOGEMON!
Man: APPARENTLY, SOME VIEWERS
HAVE CALLED OUR STATION,
CLAIMING TO HAVE SEEN MONSTERS
ON OUR NEWSCAST SCREEN.
[ GROWLING ]
THERE HE IS!
NO WAY!
MAYBE THIS IS A DREAM.
NEWS.
AUTHORITIES BELIEVE
THIS IS MERELY HYSTERIA
AMONG A FEW INDIVIDUALS.
IF YOU THINK
YOU SEE THESE MONSTERS,
YOU SHOULD SEEK
MEDICAL ATTENTION IMMEDIATELY.
THE DIGIMON ARE DRIFTING
BETWEEN BOTH WORLDS
THROUGH THAT DIMENSIONAL RIFT.
WE HAVE TO FIND IT
AND GET THROUGH
BEFORE THESE MONSTERS DESTROY
EARTH AND DIGIWORLD.
IT'LL TAKE ALL OF US TOGETHER
TO STOP THEM.
WE'VE GOT TO GET BACK.
EVEN IF WE DID,
I CAN'T HELP YOU.
IN SPITE OF ALL I'VE EATEN,
I CAN'T SEEM TO DIGIVOLVE.
I CAN'T FIGHT.
I'D JUST GET IN THE WAY.
I NEED YOU, KOROMON.
WE CAN'T WIN
UNLESS WE FIGHT AS A TEAM.
DON'T YOU GIVE UP NOW.
TAI, KOROMON, WAIT.
I WANT TO GO WITH YOU.
I TOLD YOU NOT TO LEAVE.
YOU CAN'T GO WITH US.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
PLEASE, TAI.
OH, PLEASE, PLEASE.
HUH?
OGREMON!
TAI, KARI, IT'S OGREMON...
HUH?
BUT THE PEOPLE
DON'T SEEM TO NOTICE HIM.
Tai: WHAT'S HE DOING?
HE'S JUST STANDING THERE,
WAITING FOR THE LIGHT TO CHANGE.
MAYBE IF WE WAIT,
HE'LL DISAPPEAR
LIKE THE OTHERS.
[ SNARLING ]
UHH!
ARE YOU OKAY?
KOROMON?
HUH? KOROMON,
WHERE ARE YOU?
HE'S UP THERE?
WHAT?
HE'S TRYING TO FIGHT
THAT MONSTER SINGLE-HANDED.
UHH!
[ SNARLING ]
WHOO!
UHH!
OHH!
KOROMON, DIGIVOLVE!
I CAN'T DO IT
UNLESS YOU USE THE DIGIVICE.
THE DIGIVICE ISN'T WORKING.
YOU'LL HAVE TO DIGIVOLVE
WITHOUT IT.
I JUST CAN'T.
YOU CAN DO IT, KOROMON.
AAH!
KOROMON! DIGIVOLVE!
Tai: LOOK, THE DIMENSIONAL RIFT
IS OPENING UP
LIKE A MEGA-VACUUM CLEANER.
KOROMON, HELP!
Koromon:
KOROMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
AGUMON!
HURRY, AGUMON! AAH!
MM!
[ GROWLING ]
PEPPER BREATH!
TAKE A HIKE!
AGUMON, COME BACK!
I'M NEEDED IN DIGIWORLD.
I'LL NEVER FORGET YOU,
MY FRIENDS.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
WAIT! TAKE ME WITH YOU.
YOU STILL NEED MY HELP,
AGUMON.
TAI, STAY WITH ME.
NO, GO WAIT
FOR MOM AND DAD.
I'M SO SORRY.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I KNOW YOU HAVE TO LEAVE.
I REALLY DO. OKAY?
OKAY.
AGUMON CAN'T DIGIVOLVE
WITHOUT ME.
THIS IS MY FIGHT, TOO.
PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
GOODBYE, KARI.
IT WAS REALLY HARD
TO WATCH KARI
AS I FLOATED AWAY,
BUT THERE WAS NO WAY
I COULD HAVE TAKEN HER WITH ME.
I KNEW IT WAS WAY TOO RISKY.
MOM WOULD HAVE BEEN
REALLY MAD AT ME IF I HAD,
BUT WHAT I DIDN'T KNOW
IS THAT KARI WOULD SOON FIND
HER OWN WAY TO DIGIWORLD.
Tai: AGUMON,
WE'RE BACK IN BUSINESS.
NOW WE'VE GOT TO DECIDE
WHAT OUR FIRST MOVE IS.
WELL, WE HAVE TO FIND
OUR FRIENDS.
THEN WE HAVE
TO MAKE SURE
YOU AND THE OTHERS
GET HOME SAFELY.
NOT UNTIL WE CONQUER
ALL THE EVIL DIGIMON.
OTHERWISE, NEITHER ONE OF
OUR WORLDS WILL EVER BE SAFE.