T.K.:
ME AND PATAMON WERE ALL ALONE
ON THE FLYING BED AND THEN WE LANDED
IN THIS NEATO PLACE
WHERE ALL THE BABY DIGIMONS
ARE BORN.
THEY WERE BEING PROTECTED
BY ILEKMON.
HE WAS NOT VERY NICE TO US
BECAUSE HE THOUGHT WE WERE
GOING TO HURT HIS BABIES.
PATAMON AND ILEKMON
GOT INTO A LITTLE FIGHT,
BUT I MADE 'EM STOP.
I TOLD 'EM TO PLAY TUG-O-WAR
INSTEAD OF FIGHTING
AND PATAMON WON!
ILEKMON THEN GOT NICE
AND TOLD US
WE COULD STAY
IN PRIMARY VILLAGE FOR A WHILE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT!
♪ DI-DI-DI,
DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE INTO
DIGITS OF CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE-- ♪
♪ ( bird cry ) ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON -
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
( laughing )
HEY, LET'S PLAY A GAME
WITH THE BABY DIGIMON!
I AM PLEDGED
TO OBEY YOUR COMMAND, DEVIMON.
OKAY, SO YOU DON'T WANNA
PLAY ANY GAMES.
LEOMON'S COME BACK!
BOOM BUBBLE!
WE GOTTA
GET OUT OF HERE!
YEAH!
HE'S SCARY.
LEOMON WAS ALWAYS
A GOOD DIGIMON.
I JUST WISH WE COULD
GET RID OF THE BLACK GEAR
THAT'S CAUSING HIM
TO BE SO MEAN.
T.K.:
THAT'S EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
HE'S JUST WAY TOO BIG!
Ogremon:
HELLO--YOU'VE GOT COMPANY.
YOU'RE A NICE LITTLE KID,
AREN'T YOU?
GET YOUR HIDE OUT HERE SO
I CAN GET A GOOD LOOK AT YOU!
'CAUSE IF YOU DON'T,
YOUR LITTLE FRIEND HERE
IS GONNA SQUEAK HIS LAST SQUEAK!
( digi-babies crying )
WE GOTTA SAVE 'EM!
( Patamon's thoughts: )
POOR LEOMON.
I KNOW HE WOULDN'T ATTACK US
IF THAT STUPID BLACK GEAR
DIDN'T HAVE HIM
UNDER AN EVIL SPELL.
HE'D COME OVER TO OUR SIDE
IF WE COULD ONLY FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO HELP HIM.
I GOTTA PROTECT T.K.
FROM OGREMON,
BUT HE'S SO BIG
AND I'M NOT!
( Leomon roars )
I'VE BEEN COMMANDED
BY MY MASTER
TO TAKE THE DIGI-DESTINED!
( screaming )
Garurumon:
HOWLING BLASTER!
Matt:
T.K.!!!
YOU CAME IN TIME!
THAT WAS CLOSE!
NOW YOU'VE DONE IT!
THIS LITTLE GUY'S
GONNA GET SQUISHED!
HEY--WHERE'D HE GO?
Tai:
HE'S STAYING WITH US!
OVER MY STINKY ARMPITS
HE WILL!
OH, I'M SO SCARED--
GET 'EM, GREYMON!
NOVA BLAST!
Ogremon:
DIDN'T ANYBODY EVER TELL YOU
NOT TO PLAY WITH FIRE?
SOMEONE COULD GET HURT--
NAMELY ME!
NOW TO EDUCATE YOU--
I'LL SHOW YOU WHO'S
THE HEAD HONCHO ON THIS ISLAND.
I COULD FIGHT YOU BLINDFOLDED!
( both grunting )
HHRRAH!
AARRGGHH!
THE BLACK GEARS!
( Leomon screaming )
TURN BACK OR HE'LL BEAT YOU
TO A PULP!
FIST OF THE BEAST KING!
ARE YOU OKAY?
( Garurumon groaning )
FIST OF THE BEAST KING!
UNGH!
Tai:
NO! WE NEED YOU, GREYMON!
I TOLD THE GUY
NOT TO PLAY WITH FIRE.
Devimon:
I COMMAND YOU TO BRING ME
THE DIGI-DESTINED,
STARTING WITH
THE SMALLEST CHILD!
I AM YOUR HUMBLE SERVANT
AND WILL OBEY YOU, DEVIMON.
Matt:
T.K., WATCH OUT!
WHAT NOW, MATT?
HURRY! MOVE AWAY!
BOOM BUBBLE!
Patamon:
OH NO! IT'S NOT WORKING!
OH!
( Patamon whimpering )
PATAMON!
OH! OH!
WANNA FIGHT?
HOW ABOUT A PRICKLY BANG ZOOM!
WHOA, TAGAMON!
PATAMON, YOU GOTTA
TAKE IT EASY!
I'M SORRY.
WHAT FOR?
I WAS JUST
TRYING TO PROTECT YOU.
AND YOU WERE DOIN' GREAT--
DON'T FEEL BAD, LITTLE GUY.
Izzy:
TAI, YOU ARE NEVER
GOING TO BELIEVE THIS!
WHAT'S HAPPENING, IZZY?
Izzy:
WE HAVE THE CONSUMMATE SOLUTION
TO ALL OF OUR PROBLEMS.
Tai:
THAT'S COOL,
BUT WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
CHECK 'EM OUT.
THEY CALL THEM DIGIVICES.
THEY HAVE THE CAPABILITY
TO COMPLETELY OBLITERATE
THE BLACK GEAR.
THEN LET'S GIVE 'EM A TRY.
WE HAVE NO OTHER CHOICE
RIGHT NOW--
WE HAVE TO TAKE THE CHANCE
AND STOP HIM!
Matt:
DON'T WORRY--
I GOT YOU COVERED, T.K.
Tai:
READY FOR A REAL FIGHT?
HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR,
BOOGER-BREATH?
COME ON AND GET US
IF YOU DARE!
WHAT'S UP, DUDE,
HAVE YOU TOTALLY FLIPPED OUT?
I MUST DO
AS I AM COMMANDED.
COME HERE.
AAAHHH!!!
THESE THINGS PACK QUITE A PUNCH.
( Leomon continues to scream )
HOW'D THEY DO THAT?
ROTTEN KIDS!
Izzy:
OGREMON! OVER HERE!
Kabuterimon:
YOU'VE ONLY JUST BEGUN
TO SEE OUR POWER.
ELECTRO SHOCKER!
THAT'S BAD.
IT WORKED!
WE DESTROYED THE BLACK GEARS!
WE'RE SAFE NOW--
LEOMON'S BACK TO
HIS NORMAL SELF.
HA! THOSE LITTLE FOOLS
ARE KIDDING THEMSELVES.
THEY DON'T KNOW WHO THEY'RE
DEALING WITH.
THEY'RE GONNA FIND OUT
SOONER THAN THEY THINK.
Leomon:
ACCORDING TO ANCIENT LEGEND,
OUT WORLD WILL BE TAKEN OVER
BY A STRANGE DARK FORCE
THAT WILL CHANGE GOOD DIGIMONS
INTO BAD ONES.
OUR ANCESTORS HAVE PREDICTED
THAT A GROUP OF CHILDREN
CALLED THE DIGI-DESTINED
WILL APPEAR FROM ANOTHER WORLD.
WHEN THEY ARRIVE THEY WILL
COME TO POSSESS SUPER-POWERS
THAT WILL EVENTUALLY
SAVE OUR WORLD FROM DESTRUCTION.
I BELIEVE THEIR PREDICTION
HAS COME TRUE.
FILE ISLAND HAS BEEN SEIZED
BY AN EVIL POWER.
WE'RE IN DANGER OF DESTRUCTION,
AND NOW YOU'VE APPEARED.
WHOA, THAT'S AMAZING,
BUT TELL ME,
HOW CAN YOU BE SURE THAT WE'RE
THE KIDS YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT?
YEAH, DO YOU HAVE SOME PROOF
THAT WE'RE THE SAME ONES?
IT'S BEEN FORETOLD THAT
THE DIGI-DESTINED
HAVE THE ABILITY TO MAKE
DIGIMONS DIGIVOLVE.
YOU'VE DONE THAT
AND IT'S ALL THE PROOF I NEED.
I, FOR ONE,
HOPE IT'S TRUE.
MY THEORY IS WE'LL BE RELEASED
AFTER WE SAVE THE ISLAND.
ONCE OUR PURPOSE IS SERVED,
THERE'S NO OTHER REASON
FOR US TO REMAIN.
Mimi:
AND I'LL FINALLY BE ABLE
TO CHANGE THESE CLOTHES!
THAT'S RIGHT--
IF LEOMON'S INFORMATION
IS CORRECT,
WE'LL BE HEADING
STRAIGHT FOR HOME.
I CAN'T WAIT!
HOW CAN
WE MAKE IT HAPPEN?
WE'RE NOT EVEN SURE
WHO'S CAUSING IT?
WHAT IF IT'S A FORCE
THAT'S TOO BIG FOR US TO HANDLE?
DEVIMON IS THE MAIN CAUSE
OF ALL THIS EVIL.
TO SAVE THE ISLAND,
YOU'LL HAVE TO DEFEAT HIM.
LET'S GO FOR IT.
( All moaning with dissaproval )
WHY NOT?
IF WE DON'T DEFEAT HIM,
IT'LL NEVER BE OVER.
FINE WITH ME--BESIDES,
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE FOR US TO LOSE
WITH THE DIGIVICES.
FIRST THING ON MY LIST
WHEN I GET HOME
IS TO DO SOME KILLER SHOPPING.
Palamon:
FOR THAT TO HAPPEN,
WE HAVE TO GET YOU BACK HOME.
Tentomon:
IF WE ALL WORK TOGETHER,
WE'RE SURE TO WIN.
I'M READY ANY TIME
YOU ARE, BUDDY.
HOW ABOUT IT, MATT?
ARE WE UP TO THE CHALLENGE?
IT'S GONNA BE TOUGH.
WHEN YOU GET DOWN TO IT,
WE HAVE NO OTHER CHOICE.
ALRIGHT THEN, TROOPS,
LET'S GET TO IT!
Tai:
FAR OUT! IT'S A DONE DEAL!
Leomon:
DEVIMON IS VERY POWERFUL,
HE'S BROUGHT NOTHING BUT TROUBLE
TO FILE ISLAND.
WE MUST BE CAREFUL.
PERFECT--
THAT TRAITOR LEOMON IS
LEADING THEM RIGHT INTO MY TRAP.
HE'S BEEN VERY VALUABLE TO ME.
I GUESS SO, BUT I'M LOYAL
AND BETTER-LOOKING.
LISTEN TO ME!
HUH?
YOU WILL PAY THEM
ONE FINAL VISIT.
READY?
( evil laughter )
HEAR THIS, DIGI-DESTINED--
MY POWER IS INFINITE!
YOUR HOPES AND DREAMS
ARE USELESS,
I AM THE SUPREME MASTER
OF THIS ISLAND!
IF YOU DARE TO DEFY ME,
I WILL UNLEASH THE POWERS
OF THE UNIVERSE AND CONQUER YOU!
YOU CAN'T ESCAPE!
OH NO, WHAT'S THAT?
BIG TROUBLE'S BREWING--
WE BETTER GET READY FOR ACTION.
Joe:
BLACK GEAR!
THIS IS GOING TO BE
THE BIG ONE, JOE,
IT'S TIME TO SHOW
YOUR TRUE SELF.
Sora:
YOU FEELIN' OKAY, JOE?
JUST A LITTLE SEASICK.
CAN'T TURN BACK NOW.
Mimi:
WHAT IN THE WORLD IS THAT?
Tai:
IT MUST BE DEVIMON!
I DIDN'T EXPECT HIM
TO BE SUCH A BIG GUY!
BAD GUYS ALWAYS SEEM TO THINK
BIGGER IS BETTER.
Leomon:
'FRAID NOT.
DEVIMON POSSESSES IMMENSE POWER,
SO BE CAREFUL.
HE'S HERE!
Tai:
UH, AGUMON,
YOU BETTER DIGIVOLVE.
RIGHT!
( wind howling )
( all screaming )
YOU ARE FOOLS!
DON'T EXPECT ME TO PLAY
SILLY GAMES WITH YOU,
I'M FAR TOO WISE FOR THAT!
Ikkukumon:
HARPOON TORPEDO!
AAAAH!
THAT'S A BULL'S EYE,
IKKAKUMON!
METEOR WING!
URGH!
Sora:
QUICK, EVERYBODY,
THERE'S NO TIME TO WASTE--
WE'VE GOT TO STRIKE
RIGHT AWAY!
DIGIVOLVE! YOU GOT IT.
Agumon:
READY GANG?
AGUMON DIGIVOLVE INTO...
GREYMON!!!
YEAH! GO, GREYMON!
GABUMON DIGIVOLVE INTO...
GARURUMON!!!
LET'S TURN THIS GUY
INTO PUDDING!
TENTOMON DIGIVOLVE INTO...
KABUTERIMON!!!
MY BIOLOGY TEACHER
WOULD LOVE THIS.
PALMON DIGIVOLVE INTO...
TOGEMON!
I DO LIKE THE WAY
OUR COLORS MATCH.
NOVA BLAST!
HOWLING BLASTER!
I THINK HE'S GOT HIM!
Matt:
OH NO!
YOUR ATTACKS ARE PITIFUL--
I'M AFRAID YOU'LL HAVE TO
TRY HARDER THAN THAT!
ELECTRO SHOCKER!
SO YOU WANT A NEEDLE SPRAY,
DO YOU?
GIVE UP, YOU FOOLS,
IT'S USELESS!
OH, POOR TOGEMON!
KABUTERIMON!
YOU'RE MINE, NOW!
AY-EEE!
YOU!
YOU GOT NO CHANCE AGAINST
THE LIKES OF US, KITTY CAT.
HA HA HA HA!
( Birdramon squealing )
YOU'RE NOT WORTH MY TIME!
BIRDRAMON!
OUT OF MY SIGHT!
OOH!
( screaming )
Devimon:
YOU'RE NEXT!!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
IKKAKUMON, NO!
ELECTRO SHO--
AAH!
OH BOY, THERE'S NOBODY LEFT--
WHAT DO WE DO, PATAMON?
NOW TO GET RID OF YOU--
THEN I'LL HAVE NOTHING TO FEAR.
THEY SAY THE SMALLEST
WILL DESTROY ME,
AND I'M NOT GOING TO
LET THAT HAPPEN.
DON'T MOVE--
MAKE IT EASY ON BOTH OF US.
GRRR!
T.K., RUN!
GRR!
EEEE-YA!
YOU SEEM TO FORGET--
I AM DEVIMON!
SUPREME MASTER OF THIS ISLAND!
I HAVE POWER OVER ALL DIGIMONS!
NO ONE CAN CONQUER ME!
AAAH!
( all groaning )
WHOA--THAT GUY
KNOWS HOW TO TAKE IT OUT OF YOU.
I CAN'T MOVE--
EVEN MY NEEDLES FEEL NUMB.
NOW IS PROBABLY NOT A GOOD TIME
TO TAKE A NAP.
THIS IS BAD.
T.K.:
MATT!
YOU WILL BE MINE!
HEY--GET READY TO RUN!
AAH!
POW!
WHAT'LL I DO?
T.K.'S IN DANGER,
I'VE GOTTA PROTECT HIM.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT--
IT ISN'T WORKING!
OH, WHY CAN'T I DIGIVOLVE?
PATAMON, HELP!
I'LL SAVE YOU, T.K.!
HANG ON, PAL!
( spacey sounds )
WHAT?
AAH!
HUH?
WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S PATAMON--
HE MUST BE DIGIVOLVING!
PATAMON DIGIVOLVE INTO...
ANGEMON!!!
HEY, PATAMON FINALLY DIGIVOLVED!
THAT'S SUPER-COOL!
NOT BAD--THAT LITTLE GUY
REALLY HAD IT IN HIM.
NICE HAIR--GOOD COLOR.
I WANT TO TAKE HIM
HOME WITH ME.
WHAT'S THIS?
ANOTHER FOOLISH ATTEMPT?
THE FORCES OF GOOD
ARE MORE POWERFUL--
EVEN YOU CAN'T STOP US.
I'LL DESTROY YOU
AND BRING PEACE TO THE ISLAND.
OH!
WHOA!
WOW!
THAT LIGHT IS SO BRIGHT--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO ME?
GOMAMON!
STOP IT! I'M NOT GOING TO
ALLOW YOU TO TAKE MY POWER AWAY,
YOU'LL HAVE TO FIGHT ME!
I'M AFRAID
I HAVE NO OTHER CHOICE.
IF I CAN HELP OTHERS,
MY FATE IS UNIMPORTANT.
ANGEMON!
YOUR POWERS HAVE GOTTEN
FAR OUT OF CONTROL
AND MUST BE EXTINGUISHED!
I AM READY TO FIGHT FOR PEACE!
HA HA HA!
AAH!
NOW YOU'VE DONE IT!
BE CAREFUL!
HA HA HA!
I'LL GET HIM--RELAX.
AAH!
COME HERE, PRETTY BOY!
I'LL STOP YOU!
AY-EEE!
AAH!
YOU HAVE USED UP
ALL YOUR POWER--
THAT WASN'T VERY SMART, ANGEMON.
NOW YOU'RE NO USE TO ANYONE!
YOU CAN'T GET AWAY
FROM THE DARK FORCES.
EVIL IS EVERYWHERE,
SO DON'T SAVOR YOUR VICTORY.
THERE ARE OTHER DIGIMON
JUST AS POWERFUL AS I AM.
SOME OF THEM
ARE EVEN STRONGER--
I WONDER WHAT YOU'LL DO
WHEN YOU RUN INTO THEM?
YOU HAVEN'T WON AT ALL--
WHAT A WASTE OF TIME!
HA HA HA HA!
T.K.:
ANGEMON!
T.K., I'LL COME BACK AGAIN,
IF YOU WANT ME TO.
T.K.:
ANGEMON!
T.K., I'LL COME BACK AGAIN,
IF YOU WANT ME TO.
ANGEMON!
( gasps )
Tentomon:
WHAT DO YOU KNOW--
IT'S A DIGI-EGG!
T.K.:
DO YOU THINK
IT COULD BE ANGEMON?
Gabumon:
I KNOW IT IS--
HE'S JUST RESTING FOR A WHILE
TO REGAIN HIS STRENGTH.
Palmon:
BUT DON'T WORRY--YOU'LL SEE HIM
AGAIN WHEN HE DIGIVOLVES.
T.K.:
I WILL MAKE SURE
TO TAKE REALLY GOOD CARE OF HIM.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE, ANGEMON.
HUH?
Sora:
LOOK, THE ISLAND
IS COMING BACK TOGETHER AGAIN.
Izzy:
EXACTLY--DEVIMON'S
BEEN DEFEATED.
WHEN EVIL IS ELIMINATED,
THE ISLAND RETURNS
TO ITS NORMAL STATE.
WITH DEVIMON OUT OF THE WAY,
I CAN TAKE OVER NOW!
HELLO--YOU FORGETTING ABOUT ME?
LEOMON? GET ME OUT OF HERE!
WHY CAN'T THE BAD GUYS EVER WIN?
Matt:
WHAT'S WITH THOSE OTHER
EVIL DIGIMON ACROSS THE SEA?
Joe:
YEAH, I THOUGHT
WE WERE GOING HOME.
Mimi:
I DON'T WANNA HAVE TO
FIGHT AGAIN--
I THINK I BROKE A NAIL.
Tai:
ACCORDING TO LEOMON'S LEGEND,
WE'VE GOTTA DO IT!
REMEMBER, HE SAID
WE'RE THE DIGI-DESTINED.
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING!
All:
WHOA!
AH, I'VE HEARD OF YOU KIDS.
I MUST SAY, I'M PLEASED.
EXCUSE ME, SIR,
TELL US--
WHO ARE YOU,
AND WHAT DO YOU WANT?