THE LAST THING WE NEED
IS A HOTHEAD WITH ATTITUDE.
WE GOT MORE IMPORTANT
THINGS TO THINK ABOUT.
EVERYONE'S UPSET.
LOOK, ALL I KNOW IS
THIS STUPID BICKERING
IS GIVING ME
A GIGANTIC HEADACHE.
CHILL OUT.
MATT, HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
THAT WE HAVE BEEN CHOSEN
TO BE THE DIGIDESTINED?
WOULD YOU TELL ME WHO CHOSE US
FOR THIS DUMB JOB?
I-I --
COME ON,
I WANT SOME ANSWERS,
AND YOU CAN'T SEEM
TO GIVE THEM TO ME.
YOU HAVE A POINT THERE.
DON'T WASTE YOUR TIME, JOE.
MATT'S JUST BEING
A BIG SPOILED BRAT.
YOU'RE THE BRAT.
WHY DON'T YOU GO MIND
YOUR OWN BUSINESS?
THE PROBLEM WITH YOU
IS PRETTY EASY TO FIGURE OUT.
YOU'RE UPSET BECAUSE
YOU WANT TO BE THE BOSS.
LIKE I WANT TO BE BOSS
OF THIS SORRY GROUP.
IF ANY OF YOU WANT TO
TAKE CHARGE, BE MY GUEST.
I SAY WE SHOULD TAKE CARE
OF OURSELVES.
STOP FIGHTING, YOU TWO.
WE'VE GOT TO STICK TOGETHER.
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
MATT'S THE ONE
WHO STARTED IT.
HE'S GOT A BUG
UP HIS NOSE.
HMMPH! I DON'T HAVE TO
LISTEN TO THIS.
BUG UP THE NOSE --
THAT'S BAD?
ONE MOMENT. UH!
AAH!
DON'T PUSH ME TOO FAR.
OH, I'M SCARED.
YOU HAD BETTER BE SCARED.
I'M GETTING REALLY MAD.
EXCUSE ME, BUT WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO ABOUT IT?
SO, THOSE LITTLE TWERPS
ARE ABOUT TO SELF-DESTRUCT.
I'LL JUST SIT BACK
AND ENJOY THE SHOW.
STAY RIGHT THERE!
GET REAL, DUDE.
WATCH IT! STAND BACK!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
AGUMON -- FOURTH DIGEVOLVED.
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MASTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
WARGREYMON!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
OOH!
THERE IS NO NEED
FOR US TO FIGHT.
I MUST.
AAH!
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
YOU CHICKEN?
THAT'S IT!
MATT, I'M GOING TO TELL MOM
THAT YOU WERE FIGHTING.
SORRY, T.K.,
BUT I HAVE TO DO THIS.
BOTH OF YOU,
STOP IT RIGHT NOW!
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
YOU TWO ARE JUST
MAKING THINGS WORSE.
HE'S GOT TO BE
TAUGHT A LESSON AND FAST.
HERE, TAKE THIS.
I'M ONLY DOING THIS
TO HONOR THE MEMORY
OF ALL THE BRAVE DIGIMON
THAT HAVE HELPED US.
THEY TRUSTED US AND BELIEVED
IN OUR COMMITMENT.
UH!
WE CAN'T LET THEM DOWN.
WHAT IF WE
MADE A MISTAKE?
THIS IS AWFUL.
WE HAVE TO STOP THEM.
UNFORTUNATELY,
THEY'RE MEGADIGIMON,
AND THERE'S NOTHING ANY OF US
CAN DO ABOUT IT.
THE BEST THING IS FOR THEM
TO DUKE IT OUT.
I JUST HATE FIGHTING,
AND WE CAN'T LET OUR FRIENDS
DESTROY THEMSELVES.
IT'S A DOG-EAT-DOG WORLD,
ISN'T IT?
THEY'RE NOT DOGS.
WE JUST SIT AND WATCH THEM
TAKE CARE OF BUSINESS.
OH, YEAH?
I DON'T HAVE TO LIKE IT.
GOMAMON, GET A GRIP.
THE LAST THING WE NEED
IS ANYONE FIGHTING.
HA HA HA!
I'M A GENIUS.
THEY'RE ALL GOING TO
HATE EACH OTHER.
TERRAFORCE!
YAY! GO GET THEM.
OH, BOY,
I LOVE A GOOD FIGHT.
UHH!
OH! I'VE HAD IT!
MIMI.
I'M GOING TO SIT
AND STARE AT THE FLOWERS
UNTIL EVERYBODY
STARTS GETTING ALONG.
OH, LIKE THAT'S
GOING TO HELP.
METALRAPTOR!
TERRAFORCE!
I'M NOT AFRAID.
WELL, MAYBE A LITTLE.
OH.
MY NAME'S KARI.
PLEASE TELL ME
WHO YOU ARE.
DO YOU WANT TO BE FRIENDS
WITH US?
WHAT IN THE DIGIWORLD
IS SHE DOING?
SHE APPEARS TO BE CONVERSING
WITH HERSELF.
SHE'S LOSING IT.
YOU SEEM TO BE NICE ENOUGH.
OH.
KARI!
AAH!
IZZY!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
[ SCREAM ]
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
AAH!
WHERE ARE WE?
NO IDEA.
Woman's voice:
IN THIS WORLD,
THERE IS A BALANCE
OF DARKNESS AND LIGHT.
THE LIGHT REPRESENTS
ALL THAT'S GOOD.
THE DARKNESS IS THE EVIL.
WHEN THE DARKNESS
BECOMES LARGER THAN THE LIGHT,
IT UPSETS THE BALANCE.
THE BALANCE SEEMS
REALLY OUT OF WHACK.
FIND A SWITCH
AND PUT THE LIGHTS BACK ON.
THERE'S SOMETHING OVER THERE.
OH!
I KNOW THIS
SOUNDS INCREDIBLE,
BUT COULD WE
BE HOME AGAIN?
I'VE SEEN
THAT DIGIMON BEFORE.
WHY, OF COURSE,
THAT'S PARROTMON.
HE WAS THE MYSTERIOUS DIGIMON
THAT APPEARED
IN HEIGHTEN UTARUS
APPROXIMATELY
FOUR YEARS AGO.
NOW HE'S
COMPLETELY DIGEVOLVED.
HE PASSED THROUGH
THE DIMENSIONAL DIVIDE.
SOME TIME AGO,
A DIGIEGG FELL THROUGH A HOLE
FROM OUR WORLD TO YOURS.
KARI, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I THINK KARI'S HAD
TOO MUCH CATNIP.
MY THEORY IS SOMEONE ELSE
IS USING KARI'S BODY
TO SPEAK FOR THEM.
MY WISH IS THAT THERE BE PEACE
AND HAPPINESS FOR EVERYONE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
ARE YOU SOME KIND
OF SUPERBEING OR SOMETHING?
NO, NOTHING LIKE THAT.
I AM SIMILAR TO THE DIGIMON.
I WAS PRODUCED BY DATABYTES
TAKEN FROM THE INTERNET,
BUT THERE'S A DIFFERENCE.
UNLIKE THE DIGIMON,
WE'RE UNABLE TO TAKE A SHAPE
IN THE FORM
OF A PHYSICAL BODY.
IN ORDER FOR ME
TO COMMUNICATE TO YOU,
I HAD TO BORROW KARI.
COULDN'T YOU HAVE
TAKEN JOE INSTEAD?
I HAD TO TAKE KARI.
SHE'S THE ONLY ONE I'M ABLE
TO COMMUNICATE WITH.
TO BE HONEST,
I WANTED TO CONTACT YOU
WHEN YOU ARRIVED
AT FILE ISLAND,
BUT IT WAS
COMPLETELY IMPOSSIBLE
UNDER THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
[ ALL GASP ]
WOW! IT'S A BLAST
FROM THE PAST.
THAT'S US FOUR YEARS AGO.
HEY, THAT'S ME. HOW TYPICAL.
I'M ON THE TELEPHONE.
I WAS SO CUTE.
HARD TO BELIEVE
WE WERE THAT LITTLE.
THERE'S MY BROTHER
AND ME.
THAT'S DEFINITELY ME,
BUT WHAT'S WITH THE LIGHT?
ITS PURPOSE IS TO PROCESS
ALL YOUR VITAL INFORMATION.
THAT'S KIND OF FREAKY.
WHY'S IT DOING THAT?
JUST FOLLOW ME.
I'LL EXPLAIN IT TO YOU.
[ ALL SCREAM ]
HERE WE GO AGAIN.
WHERE ARE WE NOW,
WHOEVER YOU ARE?
A RATHER BIZARRE PLACE,
INDEED.
CHECK THIS OUT.
[ ALL GASP ]
THEY LOOK LIKE DIGIEGGS.
LOOK, CRESTS AND DIGEVICES.
OKAY, THIS IS GETTING WEIRD.
OH, AND FLOATING
IN THE SKY IS NORMAL?
AAH!
OKAY, IT'S OFFICIAL.
THIS IS DEFINITELY
GIVING ME THE CREEPS.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, FELLAS,
CAN'T YOU SAY HELLO?
THESE MEN
ARE JUST COMPUTER IMAGES.
THEY ARE FIGMENTS
FROM THE PAST
WHO HAVE BEEN DIGITALLY
TRANSMITTED TO YOUR PRESENT.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THIS IS FROM
MYOTISMON'S CASTLE.
HERE'S MYOTISMON'S
SECRET PASSAGE.
[ ALL GASP ]
THOSE ARE THE ELVES
THAT MAKE THE SHOES AT NIGHT.
THEY'RE MONITORING THE POSITIVE
AND NEGATIVE FORCES
TO PRESERVE HARMONY
IN THE WORLD.
WE TOOK THE INFORMATION
THAT WE SCANNED
FROM ALL OF YOU,
THEN WE CREATED
YOUR DIGEVICES AND CRESTS.
YOU DID THAT?
THAT MUST MEAN YOU'RE
THE ONES WHO CHOSE US.
IS THAT TRUE?
YES, IT IS.
TELL ME THIS,
WHAT MAKES US SO SPECIAL?
YOU MADE IT POSSIBLE
FOR GREYMON
TO SURVIVE AND DIGEVOLVE.
IT COULDN'T
HAVE BEEN ACCOMPLISHED
WITHOUT HELP
FROM YOU AND KARI.
HE DIGEVOLVED WITHOUT ME.
A DIGIMON CAN'T DIGEVOLVE
WITHOUT YOU.
IT DOESN'T WORK THAT WAY.
THE VERY FACT THAT
YOU WERE BOTH THERE
MADE HIM DIGEVOLVE
IN ORDER TO PROTECT YOU.
BUT HOW? WE WERE
JUST GOOFY LITTLE KIDS,
AND WE DIDN'T EVEN HAVE
A DIGEVICE.
A DIGEVICE IS JUST A TOOL
THAT WAS DESIGNED TO HELP
IN THE DIGEVOLVING PROCESS.
IT ASSISTS YOU BY MAKING YOU
AWARE OF YOUR POWERS.
IT'S THE SPECIAL QUALITIES IN
EACH OF YOU THAT MAKES IT WORK,
THE SAME WITH THE CRESTS.
CAN YOU TELL ME
WHAT YOUR PERSONAL CRESTS
REALLY REPRESENT?
WELL, MINE'S COURAGE.
AND THIS ONE MEANS LOVE.
SINCERITY.
MINE'S KNOWLEDGE.
RELIABILITY.
I KNOW WHAT THIS CREST
MEANS -- IT'S HOPE.
WELL, MINE IS --
UH, WASN'T IT
CALLED FRIENDSHIP?
ALL OF THAT'S TRUE,
BUT THERE'S MORE TO IT.
EVERYONE OF YOU HAS STRENGTHS
AND WEAKNESSES.
WE TOOK EACH OF
YOUR STRONGEST QUALITIES
THAT YOU POSSESSED
FOUR YEARS AGO,
THEN WE MADE A CREST
FOR THEM.
IF THAT TRAIT IS LOST,
THEN THE DIGIMON
MIGHT BECOME CORRUPTED.
HUH? THAT HAPPENED
WHEN I TRIED TO
MAKE AGUMON DIGEVOLVE
BY THROWING MYSELF
IN FRONT OF HIS ENEMY,
BUT THEN SOMETHING
WEIRD HAPPENED.
HE DIGEVOLVED
INTO SKULLGREYMON,
AND NOW I REALIZE
THAT WAS PRETTY FOOLISH.
BUT THE IMPORTANT THING IS
THAT YOU LEARNED FROM IT.
ALL THIS TIME WE'VE BEEN
RACKING OUR BRAINS
TRYING TO FIGURE STUFF OUT
ABOUT OURSELVES
THAT WE ALREADY KNEW.
THAT'S A FINE HOWDY-DO. HUH?
WHO KNEW?
I SEE WHY YOU CHOSE TAI
AND KARI.
THE REST OF US NEVER MADE
CONTACT WITH THE DIGIEGG.
SO WHY US?
WHEN WE EXAMINED
ALL YOUR DATA,
YOU HAD SOMETHING IN COMMON
WITH TAI AND KARI,
BUT WE'RE NOT QUITE SURE
WHAT IT MEANS.
ALL WE KNOW IS THAT
YOU'VE PROVEN YOURSELVES
TO BE VERY CAPABLE.
WHO DO THESE
BELONG TO, HUH?
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I HAVE A FEELING
IT'S US.
YES.
WOW! WHICH ONE'S ME?
I THINK THE ANSWER'S
IN THE CRESTS.
LOOK, THIS IS ME.
THAT'S MINE.
YES, BUT I'M AFRAID
I HAVE BAD NEWS.
THE DARK MASTERS GOT WIND
OF OUR PLAN
AND HAVE WORKED VERY HARD
TO DEFEAT US.
[ ALL SCREAM ]
SAVE YOUR BREATH.
THEY'RE COMPUTER IMAGES.
WHAT, JUST BECAUSE THOSE GUYS
ARE COMPUTER IMAGES,
WE HAVE TO SIT BACK
AND DO NOTHING?
HIS NAME IS GARDROMON.
HE'S A MACHINE DIGIMON,
AND HIS ARMOR IS CONSTRUCTED
OF SOLID IRON.
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING CAN
PENETRATE THAT CAN OF BEANS.
HERE COMES SOME MORE
OF THEM!
THIS IS NO SPACE-AGE
VACUUM CLEANER.
MEET MECHINORIMON.
HIS TWIN BEAM
WILL ANNIHILATE ANYTHING,
WHICH MAKES HOUSEWORK
A BREEZE.
[ ALL SCREAM ]
AAH! PIDMON IS HERE!
DON'T COME ANY CLOSER!
SHOO! GO AWAY!
RELAX. HE'S JUST AN IMAGE.
YEAH, SAVE YOUR SCREAMING
FOR THE REAL THING.
HA HA HA.
HE'S GOING TO
STEAL THE CRESTS.
OH, NO!
AH.
PIDMON,
HANDS OFF THOSE CRESTS!
GENNAI.
THAT MAN'S GENNAI?
YAAH!
HA HA HA.
AH!
FOLLOW HIM! DON'T LET GENNAI
OUT OF YOUR SIGHT!
LET'S FOLLOW AND SEE
WHAT HAPPENED IN THE PAST.
THAT'S MY DIGIEGG!
SO THAT'S WHY I WAS
BROUGHT UP ALL ALONE.
THAT EXPLAINS IT.
CHEER UP.
WE'RE TOGETHER NOW.
[ GIGGLES ]
IT'S FILE ISLAND!
AFTER GENNAI RESCUED
THE DIGIEGGS AND CRESTS,
MANY YEARS PASSED BY
UNTIL FINALLY...
I WAS BORN.
[ LAUGHING ]
OH, WOW!
I REMEMBER THAT.
IT SEEMED LIKE
I WAITED FOREVER FOR TAI.
FOR MATT.
FOR SORA.
FOR JOE.
FOR MIMI.
FOR T.K.
FOR IZZY.
WE DIDN'T THINK
THEY WOULD EVER COME.
THEN SUDDENLY,
OUT OF THE BLUE,
THEY ARRIVED WITH A BANG.
[ SCREAMING ]
HA HA HA.
TAI! OH, BOY!
[ LAUGHING ]
THE QUESTION IS,
WHAT EXACTLY ARE
THE DARK MASTERS PLANNING?
WE ARE WORKING
DAY AND NIGHT
TRYING TO FIND OUT.
FOR NOW,
ALL WE CAN DO IS GUESS
AND TRY TO OUTWIT THEM
BEFORE SOMETHING
TERRIBLE HAPPENS.
WHOA. WELL,
IF THAT'S TRUE,
WHAT SHOULD WE DO NOW?
IT'S HARD TO SAY,
BUT I BELIEVE YOU'LL ALL FIND
AN ANSWER ON YOUR OWN.
[ MOANS ]
HEY.
ARE YOU GOING TO
BE ALL RIGHT?
Kari's voice: OH, HI, THERE.
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU'VE COME BACK.
WE MISSED YOU.
DID IT HURT?
NO. WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
WELL, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
REMEMBER WHAT, TAI?
NEVER MIND, KARI.
DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT IT.
THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT HOW
WE BECAME THE DIGIDESTINED.
WE SAW IT HAPPEN.
WE SURE DID.
SO NOW THE ENTIRE WORLD
IS DEPENDING ON US,
AND WE ALL HAVE
TO SAVE IT TOGETHER.
HOW ABOUT IT, MATT?
ARE WE STILL A TEAM?
WHAT'S WRONG?
HEY, LET'S PUT
THE PAST BEHIND US.
I KNOW, BUT YOU
WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND.
SURE, I WOULD.
I SAY THAT YOU AND I
LET BYGONES BE BYGONES.
THAT'S NOT THE PROBLEM, TAI.
THIS THING IS BIGGER
THAN EITHER OF US.
IT'S NOT ABOUT RIGHT
OR WRONG.
I HAVE MY PATH
AND YOU HAVE YOURS.
I'M NOT SURE WHERE THIS PATH
IS GOING TO LEAD ME,
BUT I HAVE TO FIND IT
FOR MYSELF.
BUT I STILL BELIEVE
IN ALL OF US.
I MEAN, WITHOUT ANY OF YOU,
WHERE WOULD I BE?
THIS IS ALL
JUST SO CONFUSING,
AND I LET IT GET TO ME.
AH, THAT'S WHY WE FOUGHT.
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME,
BUT I'M GOING TO DO THIS
BECAUSE I HAVE TO.
ZUDOMON WILL BE WITH ME,
SO I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY.
IT WILL BE BETTER THIS WAY.
MATT, IF YOU
APPROACH THIS LOGICALLY,
I'M SURE YOU'LL RECONSIDER
YOUR DECISION.
YOUR CREST,
ITS THEME IS TO PROMOTE...
FRIENDSHIP, I KNOW,
BUT I HAVEN'T BEEN
TOO MUCH OF A FRIEND.
MAYBE IT'S
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW
THE TRUE MEANING OF THE WORD
OR I'VE JUST FORGOTTEN.
LET'S BREAK UP
INTO TWO GROUPS
INSTEAD OF ONE BIG ONE.
I'M SORRY, BUT I REALLY
NEED TO DO THIS ALONE.
WELL, I BELIEVE IN YOU.
I'M NOT GOING
TO STAND IN YOUR WAY.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO WITHOUT YOU?
YOU'RE A BIG KID NOW.
YOU CAN TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF, T.K.
YEAH, BUT --
WE'LL BE HERE FOR YOU.
BESIDES, YOU KNOW
HOW BIG BROTHERS ARE.
THEY NEED THEIR OWN SPACE.
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
WE'LL SEE YOU.
GOODBYE, EVERYONE.
WE'D BETTER MOVE IT,
TROOPS.
WE'VE GOT THE WORLD TO SAVE.
SO WE'RE DOWN
ONE DIGIDESTINED?
THAT'S NO PROBLEM.
WE CAN DO IT, RIGHT?
HMM? MIMI.
I'M SORRY, SORA.
I'M NOT GOING.
HUH? WHY NOT?
COME ON, WHAT?
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE
ANYBODY ELSE FIGHT
OR HURT THEMSELVES.
I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND.
THEN I'M STAYING, TOO.
BUT WHY?
IT'S NOT SAFE FOR MIMI
TO BE HERE ALONE.
I'LL MAKE SURE SHE'S OKAY,
AND THEN HOPEFULLY LATER
WE CAN REJOIN YOU GUYS, OKAY?
OKAY. GOOD LUCK, JOE.
THANKS.
WAIT FOR ME.
NOW WE'RE ALL GOING TO
BE SPLIT UP AGAIN.
JUST WHEN WE WERE
FINALLY ALL TOGETHER.
YOU MAY THINK
WE'RE SEPARATED,
BUT WE'RE REALLY NOT.
THE ROADS
MIGHT BE DIFFERENT,
BUT THE PLACE WE END UP IN
IS THE SAME.
I MEAN, THINK ABOUT IT.
IF THEY TRULY ARE
THE DIGIDESTINED,
THEY'RE DESTINED
TO BE TOGETHER ONCE AGAIN --
AT LEAST THAT'S THE WAY
I HOPE IT WORKS OUT.
Narrator: IS GATOMOM RIGHT,
OR IS THIS THE END
OF THE DIGIDESTINED?
TUNE IN TO THE NEXT
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS."