Tai: AFTER WE CLIMBED
INFINITY MOUNTAIN,
WE FOUND OURSELVES RIGHT
BETWEEN LEOMON AND OGERMON.
THEY WERE BEING
CONTROLLED BY DEVIMON,
A MOST HEINOUS CHARACTER.
DEVIMON THINKS THAT WE WERE
BROUGHT TO THE DIGIWORLD
TO DEFEAT HIM.
I THINK HE'S
SLIGHTLY CONFUSED.
WE ESCAPED WITH THE HELP
OF A WELL-TIMED DIGIVOLVE,
AND DISCOVERED A MANSION
WHERE WE ATE, CLEANED UP,
AND TRIED TO GET SOME SLEEP.
UNFORTUNATELY,
IT WAS ALL AN ILLUSION
CREATED BY DEVIMON.
HE DESTROYED
THE WHOLE ISLAND
AND SPLIT ALL US KIDS UP.
UH...I THINK WE'RE
IN TROUBLE.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
FOX KIDS WORLDWIDE AND
THE U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGI ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGI,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE
THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
Tai: THANKS TO
THAT CREEP DEVIMON,
FILE ISLAND BROKE UP,
AND ALL US KIDS
GOT SEPARATED.
NOW HE'S UP THERE
IN HIS CASTLE
ON INFINITY MOUNTAIN,
AND I HATE TO THINK
WHAT HORRIBLE THINGS
HE'S PLANNING NEXT!
[BOOM]
HEH HEH HEH HEH...
NOW THAT THEY'RE
ON THEIR OWN,
THOSE LITTLE INTRUDERS
WILL MEET THEIR DOOM!
NOTHING CAN STAND
IN MY WAY.
THE DIGIDESTIN
DON'T HAVE A CHANCE!
NOW FLY, MY PET GEARS.
FLY! HA HA HA HA HA...
Agumon: TAI,
IT'S COLD, I'M HUNGRY,
AND I WISH WE WERE
ON SOLID GROUND.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
ABOUT TO GET YOUR WISH,
BUT NEXT TIME,
BE CAREFUL
OF WHAT YOU WISH FOR!
WHOA!
YOU JUST
MIGHT GET IT!
AAAAH!
[MUMBLING]
UHHH! OK,
SO MOM WAS RIGHT.
I SHOULD HAVE WORN
A SWEATER!
HEY, WHO TURNED OUT
THE LIGHTS?
TAKE IT EASY,
AGUMON.
I'LL PULL YOU OUT.
OHHHH!
HEY, LOOK!
I FOUND MY CLOTHES.
EXCEPT THEY'RE EVEN
TOO COOL FOR ME NOW.
DON'T WORRY, I CAN GIVE YOU
THE LATEST HOT LOOK.
POI!
HEY, AGUMON,
THAT'S SMOKIN'!
NOW CAN YOU
HOOK UP MY PANTS?
HA HA HA HA!
POI!
OHH!
OHH! OHHH!
OOPS. NUKED 'EM
A LITTLE TOO LONG.
BUT LOOK
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE, TAI...
WHAT BRIGHT SIDE?
YOU WON'T BE COLD ANYMORE!
Tai: WHAT? MAILBOXES?
AGUMON, MAYBE PEOPLE
REALLY LIVED HERE
AT ONE TIME.
I WISH WE COULD MAIL
OURSELVES HOME,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE
THE ONLY WAY
WE'LL EVER
LEAVE FREEZELAND
IS TO TAKE A REAL LONG,
COLD SWIM
BACK TO INFINITY
MOUNTAIN
AND I HAVE
A FEELING THAT
IF THE MOUNTAIN IS
DRIFTING FARTHER
AND FARTHER AWAY,
THEN OUR FRIENDS
ARE, TOO.
THEY MUST ALL BE OUT THERE
ON THOSE OTHER ISLANDS.
WHERE WILL WE END UP
IF WE JUST KEEP ON
DRIFTING AROUND
LIKE THIS, TAI?
WHY WOULD I KNOW THAT?
BECAUSE YOU'RE
FROM ANOTHER WORLD,
TAI.
I'VE NEVER LEFT
FILE ISLAND.
BUT, AGUMON, I'VE NEVER
LEFT MY WORLD EITHER.
WELL, I GUESS
IT COULD BE WORSE.
THERE COULD BE
EVIL DIGIMON
ATTACKING US.
IT'S TOO QUIET HERE.
[CRASH]
AHHH...FRIGIMON!
AHHH!
FRIGIMON?
I'VE HEARD
OF THE FOOD-FRIENDLY
SNOWMON,
BUT HE'S A GENTLE
MONSTER!
WELL, DON'T LOOK NOW,
BUT HE'S ABOUT TO GENTLY
SQUASH US FLAT.
UNH!
AAAH!
OH, NO, MY BELLY'S
FREEZING!
OOOH!
IT'S A BLACK GEAR!
[GROWLS]
Together: THE BLACK
GEAR'S CONTROLLING HIM!
SUBZERO
ICE PUNCH!
AAAH!
Agumon:
HEY, DID YOU SEE THAT?
DID I? HIS PUNCH FROZE
THAT MAILBOX SOLID!
I GUESS I BETTER
HEAT THINGS UP!
PEPPERBREATH!
HA!
FRIGIMON!
I REALLY HOPE YOU HAVE
A BACKUP PLAN.
SUBZERO
ICE PUNCH! AAH!
YEAH, RUN!
AAAAH!
IF HE TOUCHES US,
WE'RE GONNA BE
ICE CUBES!
YOU'RE RIGHT!
AND I'M SO HUNGRY,
I DON'T HAVE
THE STRENGTH
TO DIGIVOLVE.
AAAAH!
WHOA!
COME BACK HERE
AND FIGHT FRIGIMON!
AAAAAH!
HUH? UH-OH.
UH-OH.
GOING SOMEWHERE?
HA HA HA HA HA...
Tai: WE'RE TRAPPED
LIKE ICE MICE!
THERE'S NOWHERE ELSE
TO RUN!
Together:
OOH, AHH!
AAAAH!
AAAH!
FRIGIMON!
HA HA HA HA...
I'VE GOT
AN IDEA, TAI.
PICK ME UP,
AND THROW ME AT HIM.
IF I CAN LAND
RIGHT ON HIS BACK,
I CAN VAPORIZE
THAT BLACK GEAR
WITH MY
PEPPERBREATH.
UNH...
I DON'T KNOW
IF THIS IS GONNA
WORK, DUDE.
I CAN BARELY
LIFT YOU,
MUCH LESS
THROW YOU,
TUBBYMON.
IT HAS TO WORK, TAI.
IT'S OUR ONLY CHANCE.
AAH! SUBZERO
ICE PUNCH! AAAH!
Tai: HE REALLY LIKES
TO BURY HIMSELF
IN HIS WORK.
ALL RIGHT,
NOW'S OUR SHOT.
ROLL UP INTO A BALL.
YOU MEAN LIKE THIS?
YEAH. NOW I'LL SHOW YOU
WHY I'M MY SOCCER TEAM'S
BEST STRIKER!
AAAAH!
HEY, UNH!
POI!
AAAHH! AAH! AAH!
WHOO!
Agumon:
YAHOO! WE DID IT!
UHH. WHAT AM I
DOING LAYING HERE?
WHAT HAPPENED?
A BLACK GEAR
WAS ON YOU,
AND YOU ALMOST TURNED US
INTO ICE SCULPTURES.
OH, I'M SO SORRY.
I JUST HATE
WHEN I DO THAT.
BUT THANK YOU
FOR DESTROYING
THE GEAR.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE BOTH
ALL RIGHT.
HAVE YOU SEEN
ANYONE ELSE HERE?
SOME MORE KIDS LIKE ME?
HMMM. COME
TO THINK OF IT,
I DID SEE ANOTHER
BOY LIKE YOU.
HE WAS
WITH A GABUMON.
THEY FELL
ONTO THAT OTHER
ISLAND OVER THERE.
YOU SAW
GABUMON?
AND MATT!
PERFECT. MATT WOULD LAND
THAT FAR AWAY.
IT'S TOO COLD TO SWIM,
AND WE'RE DRIFTING
AT 100 MILES A YEAR.
YOU'RE A WEIRD KID,
BUT, SINCE YOU GOT
THAT BLACK GEAR OUT
OF MY ACHING BACK,
I'LL HELP YOU GET
ACROSS THE WATER.
SUBZERO ICE PUNCH!
HEY, IT'S
AN ICE BRIDGE!
NOW WE CAN WALK
TO THE ISLAND!
I HOPE
YOUR PUNCHES
DON'T...
UH, YOU KNOW...
FREEZE UP?
DON'T WORRY.
AS LONG AS IT'S COLD,
I'M FULL OF PUNCH.
YEAH, BABY.
WHAT IF THE ICE BREAKS
WHILE WE'RE OUT THERE?
WE COULD BE
SEADRAMON BAIT!
UHH...AAH!
WHOA!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WE GET IT!
QUIT SHAKING UP
THE WHOLE ISLAND!
MAN, DOES EVERYBODY
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
ALWAYS HAVE
TO BE SO NOISY?
COME ON, GUYS.
LET'S START WALKING!
Matt:
T.K.! T.K.!
T.K.,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
[COUGHS]
MATT! OH!
WHERE ARE YOU, T.K.?
MATT, YOU MUST SAVE
YOUR STRENGTH!
OH... [COUGHS]
WAIT!
LOOK, MATT.
THERE'S A CAVE
RIGHT OVER THERE.
LET'S GO IN AND GET WARM
UNTIL THE STORM'S OVER.
UHHH! A CAVE!
OF COURSE!
THAT'S WHERE
T.K. IS! YES!
T.K.!
HUH?
Gabumon:
I'M SORRY, MATT.
DON'T GIVE UP
HOPE.
I WAS SO SURE
HE'D BE IN HERE.
BUT THEN AGAIN, T.K.
NEVER LIKED CAVES THAT MUCH.
AAAH...CHA!
THERE NOW. COME AND SIT
BY THE FIRE.
YOU CAN'T HELP T.K.--NOR
ANYONE FOR THAT MATTER--
IF YOU GET SICK.
YOU MUST REST
TO STAY STRONG.
NO, I GOTTA GO
BACK OUT THERE
AND FIND HIM.
I FEEL FINE!
[COUGHS]
OH, SIT DOWN.
YOU'RE NOT
LEAVING THIS CAVE.
HEY!
I'LL GO LOOK
FOR T.K.
HUH?
HEY, COME ON, MATT.
I'M YOUR DIGIMON,
REMEMBER?
I'M HERE TO HELP YOU
THROUGH THICK AND THIN,
WHETHER IT'S HOT OR COLD.
HA HA. BESIDES, I'VE GOT
A BUILT-IN WARM FUR COAT
WHICH YOU HAVEN'T.
HA HA HA HA. COME ON.
JUST SIT RIGHT HERE
AND GET WARM.
I MEAN IT.
I'LL BE BACK
IN 2 SHAKES
OF A DIGITAIL!
[COUGHS]
OHHH.
[THINKING]
POOR LITTLE T.K.
IT'S JUST NOT RIGHT.
HE'S MY LITTLE BROTHER.
I SHOULD BE THE ONE
OUT THERE LOOKING FOR HIM.
T.K.!
HEY, DAD,
ARE WE THERE YET?
Tai: HUH?
SORRY. I JUST HAD
TO SAY THAT.
SUBZERO ICE PUNCH!
MAN, THAT ISLAND'S JUST
AS FAR AWAY AS EVER.
LET'S TAKE 5, YOU GUYS,
AND THEN WE'LL
KEEP ON GOING.
THE ISLAND'S
STILL MOVING.
IF WE STOP,
WE MAY NOT BE ABLE
TO CATCH UP WITH IT.
AGUMON, IF YOU COULD
FLY LIKE BIRDRAMON,
WE'D BE THERE
ALREADY.
HMMPH.
WELL, I CAN'T.
BIRDRAMON
PROBABLY CAN'T FLY
IN THE COLD ANYWAY.
NO ONE TOASTS
MY CLOTHES LIKE YOU.
COME ON, LAUGH!
NO WAY.
OH, I HATE TO SEE
FRIENDS FIGHT.
I'LL CARRY YOU BOTH
ACROSS. LIKE THIS.
THERE. NICE AND COMFY?
YEAH. COMFY AS
A MACKEREL ON ICE.
BUT AT LEAST
WE'LL STILL BE
NICE AND FRESH
WHEN WE GET THERE.
HEY, DID I EVER TELL YOU
ABOUT THE PARTY
I WENT TO
THAT THE NUMEMONS
CRASHED? HA.
NOW, THAT'S A PARTY
NO ONE WILL FORGET.
WELL, NO SIGN OF T.K.
OUT HERE ANYWHERE.
OH, MATT'LL BE
SO DISAPPOINTED.
OHHH! MATT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT?
I TOLD YOU NOT TO LEAVE!
UHHH.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
MATT!
HE'S FROZEN.
I HAVE GOT
TO WARM HIM UP,
OR ELSE...
OR ELSE HE WILL
NEVER MAKE IT.
BUT HOW?
ALL I HAVE IS MY OWN FUR,
AND...
HEY, THAT'S IT!
WHY NOT? NO ONE'S HERE
TO SEE ME.
THERE. HERE YOU GO,
MY FRIEND.
YOU'LL FEEL BETTER
IN NO TIME.
GOOD THING
WE'RE ALONE HERE.
THIS ONE NUMEMON KEPT
FOLLOWING MY SISTER,
BUT I HANDLED IT. HA HA.
A LITTLE SUBZERO
ICE PUNCH SHOW-AND-TELL.
HEY, YOU TWO, WAKE UP!
WE'RE HERE!
YAY!
HOORAY!
UNH.
I WONDER WHERE GABUMON
AND MATT LANDED.
HMMM.
RIGHT IN THE
MIDDLE, I THINK.
SO THEY MUST
BE UP THERE
SOMEWHERE.
IN--IN THAT
FOREST.
Tai: SURE,
LET'S GO FOR A HIKE.
THEN AFTER THAT WE'LL HIKE.
THEN WE CAN HIKE SOME MORE.
SHEESH.
HEY, THERE'S A BED.
MATT MUST BE
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE!
MATT!
MATT! CAN YOU
HEAR ME, MATT?
OH, GABUMON!
MATT! I'M HERE!
MATT!
GABUMON!
MATT! ARE YOU OUT THERE?
[TEETH CHATTERING]
HUH?
GABUMON.
YOU TOOK OFF YOUR FUR
FOR--UH, UH, WELL,
THANKS.
YEAH, UH,
IT'S GOOD TO SEE
YOU'RE UP
AND FEELING...
[SNEEZES]
BETTER.
MMMM.
HEY, YOU KEPT ME
ALL WARM,
BUT NOW YOU HAVE
MY COLD.
BET YOU LOOK
PRETTY FUNNY
WITH NO FUR
ON, GABUMON.
HA HA HA.
THANKS.
IT'S OK.
MATT! GABUMON!
HEY!
IT'S TAI AND AGUMON!
THEY'RE HERE--
[SNEEZES]
MATT!
HEY!
TAI!
HA HA HA.
I THOUGHT WE'D
NEVER FIND YOU GUYS!
IT SURE IS LUCKY
THAT WE MET UP
WITH FRIGIMON.
FROSTY THE SNOWMON
HERE?
YUP, THIS IS HIM.
HE HAPPENED
TO SEE YOU TWO FALL
ON THIS ISLAND,
AND THEN HE GOT US
HERE IN NO TIME.
UH, SUBZERO ICE PUNCH,
YOU KNOW.
DID YOU SEE
ANYONE ELSE?
NO,
WHEN IT RAINS KIDS
I USUALLY NOTICE.
YOU WERE THE ONLY 2
WHO FELL HERE.
IF THERE ARE MORE
OF YOU,
THEY MUST BE
ON THE OTHER
ISLANDS.
POOR T.K.
HEY, DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL FIND HIM.
AAHHH...
CHOO!
HEY, WATCH IT, DUDE.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I AM NOT USED
TO HAVING A COLD.
[MUFFLED SNEEZE]
A COLD, HUH?
I HAVE AN IDEA.
DON'T GO, FRIGIMON.
YOU CAN'T CATCH
HIS COLD.
YOU ALREADY ARE!
[SNEEZE]
HOW'D YOU GET SICK?
YOU'RE THE ONE
WITH THE FUR
AROUND HERE. HUH?
STOP MAKING FUN
OF HIM.
LEAVE HIM
ALONE, TAI!
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU
CHILL OUT, MAN?
I WAS ONLY TRYING TO SEE
HOW WE COULD HELP HIM.
[SNEEZES]
[SNIFF]
GABUMON, I THINK
YOU OUGHT TO GO
TAKE A REST
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
[SNIFF]
WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT WE'RE GOING
TO DO NEXT.
WELL, ISN'T IT
OBVIOUS?
WE HAVE TO GO
SEARCH FOR ALL
THE OTHERS.
YEAH, RIGHT, BUT HOW ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO THAT?
YOU HEARD
WHAT FRIGIMON SAID.
EVERYONE LANDED ON
DIFFERENT ISLANDS.
UNLESS YOU'VE GOT
AN AIRPLANE
STASHED AROUND HERE
SOMEPLACE,
I THINK WE'RE STUCK.
HMMPH.
SO I GUESS WE'LL
ASK FRIGIMON
FOR HELP.
WEREN'T YOU
LISTENING TO ME?
HE SAID THEY'RE SCATTERED
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
HE ONLY HAS 2 ARMS.
HE'S NOT AN OCTOPUS.
THEN I'LL HAVE
TO MAKE A RAFT
OUT OF SOME
OF THESE TREES, OK?
MATT, CALM DOWN.
WOW, WHAT'S
EATING YOU, DUDE?
I'M ON YOUR SIDE.
I'LL HELP YOU GET OFF
THIS ISLAND
IF WE HAVE
TO BUILD SURFBOARDS, OK?
LOOK, THE OTHERS
WILL BE FINE
WITHOUT US FOR NOW.
WE GOTTA FOCUS
ON THE REAL DEAL.
"REAL DEAL"?
WHAT? I GOTTA
SPELL IT OUT FOR YOU?
WE GOTTA KNOW
IF THIS ISLAND'S
MOVING TOWARD
THAT PLACE DEVIMON
TALKED ABOUT.
THAT'S NOT
THE REAL DEAL!
YOU DOOFUS! THERE'S
NOTHING MORE REAL
THAN OUR FRIENDS
AND FINDING THEM
AND GETTING US ALL
BACK HOME SAFE,
AND DON'T YOU EVER
FORGET IT!
YOU WANT TO DITCH
YOUR FRIENDS
TO GO LOOK
FOR SOME FARAWAY
LAND, GO AHEAD,
BUT I'M NOT COMING!
I'LL FIND T.K.!
I'LL FIND ALL
OF THEM!
BY MYSELF!
BUT, MATT!
HEY, COME ON!
DON'T FREAK OUT ON ME!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
YOU'RE NOT GETTING AWAY
THAT EASY!
WHOA...UNH!
NOBODY RUNS AWAY
WHEN I'M STILL TALKING.
NOW LISTEN! MAYBE
THERE'S SOMETHING
ACROSS THE OCEAN
TO HELP US
FIND THE OTHERS!
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO GET
SO BENT OUT OF SHAPE?
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL, MATT.
UNH!
OHHH!
YOU HAVEN'T GOT
A CLUE HOW I FEEL, TAI.
YOU'RE ACTING LIKE
SUCH A JERK!
WHO ARE YOU CALLING
A JERK, JERK?
AAAH!
UNH!
TAI, STOP THAT!
YOU HAVE TO WORK
TOGETHER, GUYS!
STOP FIGHTING!
MATT, TAI!
QUIT IT!
WHAT DO WE DO?
WE HAVE TO STOP THEM
SOME WAY.
UNH!
AAH!
UH...WHOA!
AAAAH!
IT'S T.K.
HE'S OUT THERE
ON SOME STRANGE ISLAND,
AND HE'S ALL ALONE.
THAT'S IT!
WOW!
Agumon: MATT! TAI!
GET AWAY FROM THAT CLIFF!
HUH?
WHOA!
AAAH!
MATT!
TAI!
UNH.
UNH, UNH.
I GOTCHA.
UNHH...
WHATEVER YOU DO,
JUST DON'T
LET GO
OF MY HAND.
Agumon: DON'T GIVE UP,
GUYS. HOLD ON!
AH, IT'S HOPELESS.
UH, I'M SO TIRED
AND HUNGRY NOW
I DON'T HAVE ANY
STRENGTH LEFT AT ALL.
WE'D BE OK IF I COULD
JUST DIGIVOLVE
INTO GARURUMON!
[SNEEZE]
AAAAAH!
HUH? I THINK
IT'S MOJYAMON!
THAT'S HIM, BUT HE HAS
A BLACK GEAR INSIDE HIM.
AAAAH!
Agumon:
HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
[ROAR]
All: AAAH!
OHHHH!
OHH!
HA HA HA HA.
AAAAH!
WHOA!
AAAH!
OHHH!
WHOA!
UNH!
OHH!
OHHH!
IT'S RAINING KIDS
AND DIGIMON AGAIN.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO START
CARRYING AN UMBRELLA.
Gabumon and Agumon:
THANK YOU, FRIGIMON!
GOOD TIMING!
WITHOUT YOU, WE'D BE
FLAT AS PANCAKES!
HA. WELL, NEXT TIME,
TRY NOT TO LAND ON MY HEAD.
HERE, I BROUGHT SOME FOOD.
EXCELLENT!
UNH! LET'S EAT!
MMMM...
AND IT'S GOOD
AND TASTY,
JUST THE WAY
I LIKE IT.
AN OLD COLD REMEDY.
[SNEEZES]
UH, UH...
BL-BL-UHHH!
[ROAR]
AAAAH!
I'LL TAKE CARE
OF MOJYAMON.
[ROAR]
FRIGIMON!
HYAH!
UNH!
[ROAR]
SUBZERO
ICE PUNCH!
AAAAAH!
HUH?
[ROAR]
AAAAH!
BOOMERANG BONE!
WAAAH!
All: UHHH!
NICE TRICK,
MOJYAMON.
NOW WATCH OURS!
AGUMON,
DIGIVOLVE TO...
GREYMON!
GABUMON,
DIGIVOLVE TO...
GARURUMON!
[ROAR]
[GROWLS]
THAT'S IT,
GARURUMON!
GO, GREYMON!
NOVA BLAST!
AAAAH!
[GRUNTS]
Garurumon: YOU'RE NOT
PLAYING NICE!
[ROAR]
[GROWLS]
NOW, GREYMON! AIM
FOR THE BLACK GEAR!
Tai: RIGHT!
NOVA BLAST!
WHOA-OH-OH-OH!
UNH.
YOU DID IT, GREYMON!
WHEW. NOW,
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
BACK DOWN TO STANDARD
MOJYAMON SIZE.
GARURUMON, WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING AT?
[ROAR]
Matt: WOW, JUST LOOK
AT ALL THOSE BLACK GEARS.
THERE'S A MOUNTAIN OF THEM.
WHOA. I FEEL LIKE
I WAS JUST RUN OVER
BY A MONOCHROMON.
A BLACK GEAR
WAS CONTROLLING
YOU, MOJYAMON.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE FIGHT WASN'T
YOUR FAULT.
WHOA.
THE SAME THING
HAPPENED TO ME.
IT'S OK, THOUGH.
NO ONE GOT HURT.
THIS DOESN'T
CHANGE ANYTHING, TAI.
WE STILL HAVE TO GO
FIND THE OTHERS.
[GEARS SPARK]
HUH?
Agumon: LOOK, THE GEARS
HAVE FIXED THEMSELVES!
Gabumon:
IT MUST BE DEVIMON!
Matt:
AND THE ISLAND'S
MOVING AGAIN.
HEY!
Tai: WE'RE MOVING
ALL RIGHT.
THE OTHER WAY!
BACK TOWARD
INFINITY MOUNTAIN!
AND DEVIMON.
IF THAT'S TRUE,
THEN THIS IS NO TIME
FOR US TO BE FIGHTING.
MM-HMM.
HA HA HA.
NO STINKIN' GEARS
ARE GONNA STOP US!
YEAH! TOGETHER WE'RE
GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
Matt: AND NOW I KNOW
MY LITTLE BROTHER
WILL BE ALL RIGHT,
'CAUSE HE HAS PATAMON
TO TAKE CARE OF HIM
WHEN I CAN'T BE THERE.
AND I THINK AS LONG AS
WE CAN ALL TRUST EACH OTHER,
TOGETHER IT'S A SURE BET
THAT WE'LL BE ABLE
TO FIGHT AND BEAT DEVIMON!