WE FOUND ANDROMON TRAPPED
INSIDE A MYSTERIOUS FACTORY.
AFTER HE WAS FREED,
HE BECAME A DESTRUCTIVE MANIAC.
I DISCOVERED A CHAMBER WITH
A COMPUTER PROGRAM THAT RAN
THE ENTIRE FACILITY.
FORTUNATELY, MY LAPTOP INSIDE
THIS PERIMETER WAS OPERATIONAL.
ACCESSING THE MAINFRAME,
I SOMEHOW TAPPED
INTO TENTOMON'S PROGRAM.
HE DIGIVOLVED INTO KABUTERIMON
AND WITH THE HELP OF GREYMON
AND GORURUMON
HE DEFEATED ANDROMON.
APPARENTLY ANDROMON'S
PROGRAMMING HAD BEEN CORRUPTED
BY ANOTHER BLACK GEAR.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
FOX KIDS WORLDWIDE AND
THE U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGI ♪
♪ DIGIMON
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON,
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE
THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
Mimi: OF ALL THE STRANGE THINGS
THAT HAPPENED TO US ON
DIGIMON ISLAND,
I NEVER EXPECTED TO FIND
A SECRET ADMIRER
IN THE SEWER.
OK, EVERYBODY, LET'S SING
THE SONG THAT AGUMON
WROTE FOR US.
♪ DIGIMON EAT
AND DIGIMON FIGHT ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIBALLS,
FIGHT ALL NIGHT ♪
Mimi:
SINGING SURE IS FUN.
NOW LET'S TRY SOME
SOLO PERFORMANCES,
STARTING WITH MIMI.
MIMI?!
SINGING?
MERCY!
[SINGS OFF-KEY]
♪ OH, GIVE ME A HOME ♪
♪ WHERE THE BUFFALO
ROAM ♪
♪ AVOIDING YOUR DRONE ♪
HEY, COME ON!
I HAD SINGING LESSONS
FOR 3 YEARS.
OH, YOU DID?
DID IT HELP?
HA! MIMI,
YOU SHOULD GET A REFUND.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
THEN LET'S SING
AS A GROUP.
LET'S GO.
♪ DIGIMON FIGHT
AND DIGIMON FLY ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIBALL,
FIGHT ALL NIGHT-- ♪
[WEEPING]
AWW!
SORA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, WHAT'S
THE MATTER?
WELL, SOME WATER
FELL FROM UP THERE.
HUH?
AND THAT MADE
YOU SCREAM?
YEAH...NO...UH...
I USED TO SING
AT HOME.
I USED TO SING TO MYSELF
ALL THE TIME WHEN I
WOULD DO MY CHORES,
ESPECIALLY WHEN I HANG
CLOTHES TO DRY OUTSIDE,
I'D SING REALLY LOUD
'CAUSE NOBODY COULD
HEAR ME THEN.
IT'S OK TO MISS YOUR HOME,
SORA.
WHAT DO YOU MISS, TAI?
HMM?
Tai: I MISS PLAYING SPORTS,
THEN TAKING A NICE, HOT BATH.
AAH!
GAMES. MY GAMES.
I WASN'T FAR FROM
BEATING MATT ON
MY VIDEOGAMES.
BEATING ME, T.K.?
GEE, I DON'T THINK SO.
MAYBE IN YOUR DREAMS, KIDDO.
[LAUGHS]
Izzy: SO YOU DON'T MISS
ANYTHING FROM HOME, MATT?
WELL, ACTUALLY, NOW
THAT YOU MENTION IT.
I'VE BEEN DREAMING
ABOUT SUNDAY,
WHEN MOM GRILLED US
STEAKS.
MMM. MAKES
MY MOUTH WATER.
I MISS DOING MY HOMEWORK.
IF I FALL TOO FAR BEHIND,
I MIGHT HAVE TO GO
TO A JUNIOR COLLEGE.
I DON'T MISS SCHOOL.
BUT I DO MISS GOING
ON VACATION.
NOTHING BEATS HAVING
A COLD DRINK ON A SUMMER
DAY AT THE BEACH.
I JUST LOVE THE OCEAN AIR!
WHEE! THAT SOUNDS
LIKE FUN, MIMI.
IT IS.
GET A GRIP!
I MISS ACCESSING SATELLITES
TO LOOK AT THE STARS
AND PLANETS.
[SIGHS]
THEY REALLY DO COME
FROM ANOTHER WORLD.
THAT IS WHY
THEY ARE DEPRESSED.
POOR KIDS!
[SNARLING]
QUIET!
LISTEN, EVERYONE!
EYUCK!
NUMEMON.
NUMEMON?!
THEY'RE REALLY DISGUSTING
DIGIMON WHO LIVE DOWN HERE
IN THE SEWERS.
THAT'S GROSS
AND SO ARE THEY.
ARE THEY
REALLY STRONG?
NO, THEY'RE WEAK,
BUT SMELLY.
JUST WAIT TILL
THEY GET CLOSER.
AND WHAT DO YOU
SAY WE LEAVE?
OR AM I THE ONLY ONE
WHO DOESN'T WANT
TO GET STOMPED
BY STINKY SEWER
DWELLERS?
AHH!
[SNARLING]
AND THERE ARE
SO MANY OF THEM!
HURRY! RUN!
IF THEY'RE NOT STRONG,
WHY DO WE HAVE TO RUN
FROM THEM?
YOU'LL SEE.
KEEP RUNNING!
[SNARLING]
WE'RE COMING! BLAH!
Mimi: THE SEWER DWELLING
NUMEMON WERE, LIKE,
TOTALLY HYGIENE DEFICIENT.
THEY LOVED THROWING
NUMESLUDGE AT YOU
AND THEY HAD BAD BREATH, TOO.
COME ON!
LET'S KEEP MOVING!
AAH!
WE GOTTA GET OUTTA HERE!
[EVERYONE SHOUTS AT ONCE
Izzy: COME ON!
BLAH!
HEY! THIS-A WAY!
[PANTING]
[GASPS]
BLAH!
HUH?
THE ONLY THING THAT
IS ABLE TO DRIVE THEM
AWAY IS THE SUNSHINE.
WHEW!
Mimi: THANK GOODNESS.
WE FINALLY ESCAPED
THOSE NUMEMONS.
ONCE WE GOT OUTSIDE,
WE DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING
ELSE FOR MILES,
UNTIL WE SAW
THE STRANGEST THING.
AHH!
[GASPS]
Sora: THERE MUST BE
THOUSANDS OF THEM!
Izzy: I'D SAID UNDER 100.
Tai: OR MAYBE JUST 50.
Mimi: HOW DID THEY GET THERE?
I BET THERE'S ENOUGH
SNACKS TO LAST US
A LIFETIME...AT LEAST.
Matt: MIMI,
THEY PROBABLY DON'T WORK.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
THE PHONE BOOTHS?
HEY, THAT COULD BE.
I BET IT'S A TRICK, MIMI.
I WON'T ACCEPT THAT.
AHH!
EVEN IF
THEY'RE REAL,
YOU KNOW THEY'RE
NOT PLUGGED IN.
[PANTING]
MIMI!
YOU CAN'T STOP HER.
SHE'S SO STUBBORN.
YEAH, SODA!
YOU WANT ONE?
NO, I DON'T!
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BITE MY HEAD OFF!
HMM? MM-HMM.
[COIN FALLS]
[SCREAMS]
HI, CUTIE PIE. HA HA!
IT'S THEIR LEADER.
Mimi: THEIR LEADER?!
HE COULDN'T LEAD
A PACK OF SHOW POODLES,
EVEN WITH HIS DOGGY
BREATH.
HEY, LET ME TAKE YOU
OUT ON A DATE.
I THINK
HE LIKES YOU.
IT'S GOTTA BE
THE HAT.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
I WOULDN'T GO NEAR THAT
SHORT, SLIMEY, SEWER-SLIDING,
SLUDGE-SLINGER.
MIMI,
YOU'LL MAKE HIM MAD.
WHO CARES? BESIDES,
WE'RE SAFE IN THE SUNLIGHT.
[THUNDER CLAPS]
Mimi: UH-OH.
UM...WE WERE.
HOW DARE YOU CALL ME SHORT!
THE DATE'S OFF!
BLAH!
[SCREAMS]
OH, DEAR! RUN!
PARTY TIME!
[SNARLING]
[SCREAMING]
HOW DID THEY GET HERE?
WHO CARES? RUN! RUN!
RUN!
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY,
LET'S SPLIT UP.
YEAH!
HEARTBREAKER. BLAH!
OH! AHH!
JILTER! BLAH!
POISON IVY!
[SCREAMS]
WHAT?
PALMON, THANK YOU.
BUT, MIMI,
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING,
RIGHT OR WRONG.
IT'S MONZAEMON.
COME VISIT US AT TOY TOWN.
MONZAEMON LOOKS LIKE
A CUTE BIG OLD TEDDY BEAR,
BUT HE WASN'T VERY CUDDLY.
UH, PALMON,
IS HE A DIGIMON, TOO?
YES, HE'S IN CHARGE OF
A SPECIAL PLACE CALLED
TOY TOWN.
TOY TOWN IS A PLACE WHERE
HE TAKES CARE OF ALL
THE ABANDONED DIGIMON TOYS,
AND THOSE TOYS LOVE HIM.
WELL,
HE LOOKS HARMLESS.
HE ALWAYS HAS BEEN.
I MUST SAY, SO PLEASED
TO MAKE YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
ACQUAINTANCE?
HE'S ATTACKING US.
PALMON: YOU THINK?
PLEASE COME SPEND
A FUN DAY AT TOY TOWN
WITH ME.
[SCREAMS]
WHY ARE YOU RUNNING?
DID I STARTLE YOU?
SORRY.
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
HE'S NEVER ACTED LIKE THIS.
Mimi: HE IS NOW.
COME HERE, COOKIE,
I'LL PROTECT YOU.
NO, THANKS.
ON SECOND THOUGHT...
HOW ABOUT A KICKY GAME
OF SOCCER, YOU TWO?
AAH!
HE'S GONE.
SOMETHING BAD MUST
HAVE HAPPENED IN TOY TOWN.
SINCE I SAVED
YOU LADIES,
NOW WILL YOU GO
OUT WITH ME,
HUH?
NO!
OHH!
COME ON, LET'S
GO TO TOY TOWN!
BUT OUR FRIENDS?
WOW! SHE'S SO FEISTY.
WHAT A GIRL!
[PANTING]
AHH!
THERE IT IS,
MIMI, TOY TOWN.
Mimi: WOW!
IT REALLY LOOKS BEAUTIFUL.
KIND OF LIKE
A BIG AMUSEMENT PARK.
[GASPS OF AWE]
IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE ANYONE'S HERE.
SOMETHING'S
NOT RIGHT HERE.
OH, BOY. THIS IS FUN!
THIS IS REALLY FUN.
TAI?
I'M REALLY HAVING
A LOT OF FUN NOW.
FUN, FUN, THIS IS FUN!
THAT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE A LOT OF FUN.
THIS IS
SO EXCITING!
REALLY EXCITING.
JUST WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE?
ENJOY. WHAT A
DELIGHTFUL ACTIVITY.
THIS ACTIVITY IS
REALLY DELIGHTFUL.
HEY, IZZY DOESN'T TALK
LIKE THAT.
NOPE.
BOY, OH, BOY, IS THIS
REALLY GREAT OR WHAT?
[IZZY LAUGHS]
THIS REALLY ROCKS!
FORGET BOOKS!
HA HA! YOU CAN'T CATCH ME.
YOU CAN'T CATCH ME.
YOU CAN'T CATCH ME!
HA HA HA!
THAT'S WEIRD.
EVERYBODY SOUNDS LIKE
A BUNCH OF ZOMBIES.
HOW STRANGE.
THEY DO.
OH, WELL, THEY ALWAYS
WERE A LITTLE WEIRD.
I WISH I KNEW WHAT
WAS GOING ON HERE.
IT'S KIND OF CREEPY.
Agumon: HELLO!
CAN ANYONE HEAR US
OUT THERE?
HEY! HELLO, HELLO.
Agumon: CAN ANYONE
HEAR US OUT THERE?
HI, HELLO, HELLO!
WE REALLY NEED YOUR HELP.
[GASPS]
GET US OUTTA HERE!
IT'S COMING FROM
THAT LOCKED CHEST.
AGUMON,
IS THAT YOU?
YES!
ARE ALL OUR OTHER DIGIMON
IN THERE WITH YOU, AGUMON?
YES, WE'RE ALL
IN HERE.
Mimi: WHAT HAPPENED?
WE WERE RUNNING FROM
THE NUMEMON.
[PANTING]
[SNARLING]
Agumon: THEN
MONZAEMON CAME ALONG.
AAH!
[MONZAEON GROWLS]
[SCREAMS]
UGH! I THOUGHT IT
WAS ME AT TOY TOWN.
AAH! RUN!
Agumon:
WE TRIED TO FIGHT BACK.
PEPPER BREATH!
MMM.
IT'S NO USE.
MY FLAME'S NOT
WORKING. RUN!
HEARTS ATTACK!
THOSE TWO.
[PANTING]
YOU'LL SEE. TOY TOWN IS
THE GREATEST PLACE TO BE.
START THE TWISTER.
HEARTS ATTACK.
THOSE TWO.
[SCREAMS]
AT TOY TOWN,
WE JUST OOZE FUN.
SUPER SHOCKER!
BLASTER!
Mimi: GO, BABO!
[GROWLS]
HEARTS ATTACK
THEM ALL!
[MOANS AND GROANS]
SO ALL OF YOU...
WILL NOW SERVE US.
YOU'RE ALL GOING INTO
OUR COMMUNITY TOY BOX.
OUR TOY BOX IS ONLY
FILLED WITH CHILDREN.
THINKING BACK, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THIS IS GREAT. HA HA HA!
WHO NEEDS BOOKS?
THE TOYS HAVE BEEN
PLAYING WITH THEM.
AGU, TELL US,
WHAT CHANGED MONZAEMON?
Agumon:
WE DON'T KNOW.
HUH?
WELL, CAN YOU GET OUT
OF THAT BOX AND HELP?
NO, WE'RE LOCKED
INSIDE OF HERE.
IT'S UP TO YOU TWO.
YOU MUST BE THE
HEROES THIS TIME.
JUST WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Agumon: YOU MUST
DEFEAT MONZAEMON.
WHAT?
YOU'RE KIDDING!
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE CAN'T GET FREE UNTIL
YOU SAVE THE OTHERS.
[GASPS]
WE HAVE TO DO THIS!
OH, DO WE HAVE TO?
I HAVE TO TELL YOU,
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
MONZAEMON'S HEARTS
AREN'T SUPPOSED
TO ATTACK,
ONLY GIVE
HEART HUGS.
WHICH GIVE PEOPLE
SUCH A GOOD FEELING
THAT IT MAKES THEM
WANT TO HELP OTHERS.
[HUMS]
♪ YOU CAN'T CATCH ME ♪
HA HA HA!
THIS IS SO RIDICULOUS.
[CRASH]
AAH!
STOP THAT NOISE!
RIGHT NOW!
IT'S SUCH A HAPPY
DAY IN TOY TOWN!
OH, MONZAEMON!
YOU'LL LIKE THESE.
EVERYONE LIKES
THE BALLOONS.
HEY, YOU TEDDY.
WHATEVER YOU'VE DONE
TO MY FRIENDS, FIX IT!
NOW!
OR YOU'LL BE
IN BIG TROUBLE.
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
AAH!
THIS ISN'T FUNNY.
I'M BEING CHASED BY
A GIANT STUFFED BEAR.
[SCREAMS]
NO, NO, DON'T RUN
AWAY FROM TOY TOWN.
I'LL SAVE YA, HONEY!
[ROARS]
[SCREAMS]
NUMEMON.
YOU TURN HIM DOWN
AND HE STILL HELPS.
[SCREAMS]
WELL, PALMON,
WHAT CAN I SAY?
WHEN YOU'VE GOT IT,
YOU'VE GOT IT.
OH, NO! I DON'T THINK THE
NUMESLUDGE IS WORKING.
NOT YOUR BOMB!
I CAN'T WIN
THE FIGHT ALONE.
PALMON, BE CAREFUL.
TAKE THAT!
POISON IVY!
[SCREAMS]
PALMON,
PLEASE TALK TO ME.
MY POISON IVY'S
NOT STRONG ENOUGH.
[ROARS]
HEART ATTACK!
[SCREAMS]
PALMON!
TIME TO TAKE IT
TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
I MAY BE A LADY, BUT
I AM NOT A PUSHOVER.
TIME TO SHOW THIS
DIGIMON SOME MANNERS.
PALMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
TOGEMON!
YOU'RE GOING DOWN,
BIG BOY!
[ROARS]
OHH!
YOU WANT TO DANCE WITH ME?
[ROARS
[ROARS]
AAH!
UNH!
OOH!
AAH!
OHH!
DIGIMON, NEEDLE SPRAY!
AAH!
OWW!
[ROARS]
UNH!
AH, WOW!
PALMON, YOU'RE FABULOUS!
MY STEM IS BRUISED.
Mimi: AFTER EVERYONE
WAS FREE FROM THE SPELL,
AND THE TRUNK, MONZAEMON
TOLD US WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
USUALLY WHEN KIDS GET
TIRED OF THEIR TOYS,
THEY JUST ABANDON THEM.
THEY THROW THEM AWAY.
IT'S SO SAD.
SO I CREATED A HOME
FOR THESE TOYS.
THEN I WANTED TO MAKE
THE TOYS MORE IMPORTANT
TO THEIR OWNERS,
AND I FOUND A WAY
TO LET THEIR OWNERS
WALK IN THEIR SHOES.
HOW? BY TURNING KIDS
INTO ZOMBIES?
I DON'T THINK HE REALLY
INTENDED TO DO THAT, MIMI.
YOU'RE RIGHT, JOE.
I DIDN'T MEAN FOR
THAT TO HAPPEN.
AND I REALLY AM
SORRY ABOUT IT.
PLEASE ACCEPT MY APOLOGY.
I'LL NEVER DO THAT AGAIN.
REALLY!
MONZAEMON, WE KNOW YOU WOULD
NEVER HURT US ON PURPOSE.
OF COURSE NOT.
BUT AN EVIL FEELING
CAME OVER ME.
IT HAD TO BE
THAT BLACK GEAR.
YOU KNOW, I'M BEGINNING
TO TAKE THIS WHOLE BLACK GEAR
THING A LITTLE PERSONALLY.
THEY CAUSE A WHOLE LOT
OF TROUBLE BEFORE DISAPPEARING.
THAT'S RIGHT,
BUT ME AND PALMON MADE
MONZAEMON GOOD AGAIN.
YES, I THINK.
MY FRIENDS, THERE IS
ONLY ONE WAY I CAN TRULY
SHOW MY GRATITUDE,
AND THAT'S BY GIVING
YOU ALL A REAL HARD HUG.
Palmon: OH, BOY.
Monzaemon: HERE WE GO.
THIS IS MY GIFT TO YOU.
HEARTS ATTACK!
WITH A HUG!
[GIGGLING]
DUMPLING,
A KISS FOR YOUR HERO?
NO.
WOW! WHAT A GIRL!
SHE'LL COME AROUND.
[GIGGLING]