Tai: WIZARDMON WAS ABLE TO MAKE
GATOMON REMEMBER
SHE WAS TO BE DIGIMON
OF THE EIGHTH CHILD,
WHO TURNED OUT TO BE
MY LITTLE SISTER KARI.
GATOMON HAD BEEN WAITING,
AND WHEN KARI DIDN'T SHOW UP,
MYOTISMON TOOK HER
UNDER HIS GRISLY WING
AND CONVINCED HER
SHE WAS EVIL.
OUR NEW FRIENDS
TRIED TO GET THE TRUE CREST
FROM MYOTISMON'S LAIR,
BUT HE SURPRISED THEM.
GOOD NEWS IS, HE DIDN'T KNOW
KARI WAS THE EIGHTH CHILD.
BAD NEWS IS,
HE'S USING GATOMON
TO FIND OUT WHO IS.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HMM. OH, BOY.
Man: DUE TO THE CONTINUING
HEAVY FOG,
WE WILL BE EXPERIENCING
SOME DELAYS UP AHEAD.
PLEASE BEAR WITH US.
NOT AGAIN.
WHEN'S THIS GOING TO END?
Myotismon: HA!
IT'S ALMOST DONE.
HA HA HA HA HA HA HA.
SOON NOW, NOT IN FIRE
OR ICE, BUT IN FOG,
THIS WORLD WILL BE MINE!
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
Palmon: YUCK,
THIS SOIL'S POLLUTED.
[ GRUNTING ]
TASTES LIKE GASOLINE
AND OLD CANDY WRAPPERS.
I'VE GOT
THIS BOTTLED WATER.
IT'S FRESH AND PURE
AS A WINTER MORNING
IN THE SWISS ALPS.
[ GIGGLES ]
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT
IT SAYS ON THE BOTTLE.
OKAY, POUR IT ON MY ROOTS.
OHH!
MMM. YUMMY.
♪ YODELAY-HE-HOO ♪
MMM. HA HA HA. MMM.
[ GRUNTING ]
HUSH!
HMM?
MIMI, IS THAT YOU?
MIMI, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING OUT HERE?
[ GRUNTS ]
OH, HI, DAD.
YOU SHOULD BE INSIDE.
WELL, YOU SEE...
UH, I WAS JUST WAITING
FOR YOU.
[ GRUNTS ]
HA HA.
HUH?
Mimi: SO, DAD, WHY ARE YOU
SO LATE, ANYWAY?
IT'S THIS FOG.
IT'S GOT EVERYTHING
TIED UP IN KNOTS.
SAY, WHAT'S THAT YOU GOT
UNDER YOUR HAT THERE?
OH, IT'S JUST, UH, UH --
OOH! BRR! IT'S GETTING
COLD OUT HERE.
WE BETTER HURRY UP
AND GET HOME
OR MOM WILL BE WORRIED.
Woman: HI, HONEY.
Mr. Tachikawa: HELLO.
[ GRUNTS ]
SORRY. I COULD HAVE
PRETENDED YOU WERE MY DOLL
OR A STUFFED ANIMAL
I SUPPOSE,
BUT I HAVE A REPUTATION
FOR GOOD TASTE TO MAINTAIN.
I'M IN BAD TASTE?
IS THAT WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING?
OH, PALMON, I DIDN'T
MEAN IT THAT WAY.
REALLY.
I MADE
THIS DISH UP MYSELF.
I CALL IT
"SHRIMP FRIED RICE
WITH WHIPPED CREAM
AND STRAWBERRIES."
YOU'VE REALLY OUTDONE
YOURSELF THIS TIME, HONEY.
YOU MEAN IT?
I'M SO GLAD YOU LIKE IT!
I MEAN IT.
REALLY.
Boy: I CAN'T BELIEVE
I GOT A "C."
THERE GOES MED SCHOOL.
MY DAD WANTED ME
TO TELL HIM MY GRADES.
Boy #2: FORGET MYOTISMON.
THIS IS A REAL DISASTER!
THIS GRADE IS THE RESULT
OF ALL THE STRESS
FROM THE MONSTER ATTACKS.
WELL, IF YOU CAN'T GET
INTO MEDICAL SCHOOL,
I'D TRY POLITICS.
Boy: OH, NO!
GIVE ME A BREAK.
COME ON.
HUH?
[ GRUNTING ]
OH, MAN. RIGHT WHEN IT WAS
ABOUT TO GET TO THE BEST PART.
HMM.
[ BOY PANTING ]
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON,
CHARLIE?
YOU'RE AWAKE! I WAS
JUST COMING TO GET YOU.
THE WHOLE SYSTEM'S
GONE DOWN --
TRANSMITTERS, SATELLITE FEED,
THE WHOLE SHEBANG!
WHAT?
IT'S LIKE THE GODZILLA
OF ALL SYSTEMS GLITCHES,
BUT WE CAN'T CHECK IT OUT
BECAUSE COMMUNICATIONS ARE DOWN.
IT'S LIKE THE END OF THE WORLD
OR SOMETHING!
Myotismon:
HA HA HA HA HA!
NO ONE WILL ESCAPE --
NO ONE,
NOT EVEN THE EIGHTH CHILD!
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
Man: DUE TO A SYSTEMS FAILURE,
ALL TRAINS
WILL BE DELAYED INDEFINITELY.
WE APOLOGIZE
FOR THE INCONVENIENCE.
Man #2:
I GOT TO GET HOME.
THE PAY PHONES
DON'T WORK EITHER.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
EVERYTHING'S FALLING APART.
IT COULD BE WORSE.
WE COULD BE STUCK ON THE TRAIN.
Charlie: EVERYTHING
STARTED GOING WONKY
EVER SINCE
THAT FOG CAME IN.
Woman: EVEN MY CELL PHONE
ISN'T WORKING.
OF COURSE, IT WASN'T WORKING
BEFORE, BUT STILL.
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO EARN MY PAY.
TO INVESTIGATE THIS THING.
THAT'S WHAT I DO, AFTER ALL.
WE'LL COME WITH YOU.
Man: BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
SAY IT --
"I BELIEVE IN ME." GOOD!
HEY, TAI?
DO YOU THINK
GATOMON'S OKAY?
SURE, SHE IS, KARI.
FIRST THING TOMORROW,
WE'LL GO FIND HER.
I THINK WE HAD BETTER
GO TO BED.
WE'LL NEED OUR REST
TO FIGHT MYOTISMON.
DON'T WANT TO FALL ASLEEP
ON THE JOB, DO YOU?
OKAY.
YOU SCARED, KARI?
NOT REALLY.
ATTA GIRL.
LEAVE EVERYTHING TO ME.
I'M DYING
MY CLOTHES PINK AGAIN.
OKAY.
LOOKS LIKE DAD'S
WORKING LATE AGAIN.
SOMETHING WEIRD'S
GOING ON.
[ CROWD YELLING ]
Man: WE'RE JUST
DOING OUR JOB.
THE FOG'S DISRUPTING
OUR ENTIRE AREA.
WHY ISN'T ANY OTHER PART
OF TOWN SEEING FOG?
IT'S LIKE SOME ALIEN POWER
IS CONTROLLING THE FOG BANK
WITH MAGIC OR SOMETHING.
MAGIC? STOP TRYING
TO SCARE ME.
AAH!
KEEP QUIET.
[ GROWLING ]
WHAT'S THAT?
SHH. KEEP IT DOWN.
YOU BOTH SAW IT?
MM-HMM.
GOOD. AT LEAST I KNOW
I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE
GOING CRAZY.
WHAT'S THE CONNECTION?
SOMEHOW,
THE FOG'S TIED IN
WITH THESE MONSTERS
WE KEEP SEEING.
AAH!
LET THE HUMANS SCREAM.
IT DOESN'T BOTHER US EZAMON.
WE TRAVEL IN PACKS
CREATING TERROR,
WHETHER ON LAND
OR UNDER WATER.
EVERYONE, GET IN THE CAR!
[ SCREAMING ]
Man: AN IMPENETRABLE FOG
HAS SEALED OFF
THE MAIN DISTRICT
OF THE CITY.
INCOMING REPORTS ALSO VERIFY
THAT ALL COMMUNICATIONS SYSTEMS
APPEAR TO HAVE BEEN
RENDERED USELESS.
I'M COMING, MATT!
T.K.!
I HAVE TO GO!
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHATEVER HAPPENS,
THEY'LL NEED ME THERE.
OH, MOM.
MATT IS THERE,
AND SO IS DAD.
WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE THEM.
OH.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
WE'LL GO TOGETHER.
GET YOUR COAT, SON.
YEAH!
WAKE UP, SON.
GET UP AND GET DRESSED.
UH, WHAT IS IT?
DAD, WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
I'LL TELL YOU LATER.
JUST GET UP
AND GET DRESSED, OKAY?
[ CROWD TALKING ]
Woman: JOE,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
DOWN TO THE PIER.
MAYBE WE CAN GET IN
BY BOAT.
Man: AN ANNOUNCEMENT
WILL BE MADE
WHEN SERVICE HAS BEEN RESTORED.
WE APOLOGIZE
FOR ANY INCONVENIENCE.
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
I'M PHANTOMON.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE NEAR ME
OR MY FRIGHTENING
LITTLE FRIENDS
WHEN I START TO SWING
MY SHADOW-SCYTHE.
MYOTISMON
REQUESTS YOUR PRESENCE,
AND HE WON'T TAKE "NO"
FOR AN ANSWER.
ARE YOU REALLY GOING
TO SOCCER PRACTICE TODAY?
TAI WILL BE THERE,
AND I REALLY NEED
TO TALK TO HIM
ABOUT OUR PLAN OF ATTACK.
BESIDES, I COULD USE
THE PRACTICE.
MOM, I'M GOING TO SOCCER.
MOM?
WELL, I'LL SEE YOU
IN A LITTLE BIT.
OH, GREAT.
THE PHONE'S STILL OUT.
Woman:
OH, YOUR POOR FATHER.
I HOPE HE'S NOT STUCK
IN THE SUBWAY.
WE'RE NOT WATCHING
THAT VIDEO AGAIN.
THE TV's STILL OUT,
SWEETIE.
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
I WONDER WHO'D BE
DROPPING BY UNANNOUNCED.
COMING!
HELLO? AAH!
PEPPER BREATH -- POI!
AGUMON!
TAI!
AAH!
MOM!
Man: RUN THIS WAY!
HURRY! [ SCREAMS ]
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE ALL SAFE NOW.
BUT, HONEY,
WHAT ARE THEY?
IT'S A LONG STORY, MOM!
AAH!
GARO TWISTER!
YOU JUST TALKED.
I SAW YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
A STUFFED ANIMAL.
WELL, LIFE'S FULL
OF SURPRISES.
WHERE'S THE SOCCER FIELD?
IT'S DOWN AT THE SCHOOL.
WHY DO YOU ASK?
ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW
IS SORA'S IN TROUBLE.
I'VE GOT TO FIND HER.
OH.
Phantomon: WE'LL START
BY SEPARATING THE CHILDREN
FROM THEIR PARENTS.
AH, HOW THEY'LL SCREAM
AND WEEP -- DELICIOUS.
[ MONSTERS LAUGHING ]
I GUESS YOU'RE NOT
AS POWERFUL
HERE IN THE REAL WORLD
AS YOU THOUGHT YOU'D BE.
POWER ISN'T ANYTHING
I'D CONCERN MYSELF WITH
IF I WERE YOU, ESPECIALLY
SINCE YOU DON'T HAVE ANY,
YOU LITTLE TRAITOR.
NOW WILL YOU TELL ME
WHAT HAPPENED, DAD?
I HARDLY KNOW MYSELF,
BUT I WANT YOU
TO STAY HERE, OUT OF SIGHT.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
THE STATION, TO TRY TO FIND
SOME WAY TO COMMUNICATE
WITH THE OUTSIDE WORLD --
SMOKE SIGNALS, ANYTHING.
YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE.
STAY WITH GABUMON.
HOW DO YOU
KNOW ABOUT ME?
BUT, DAD, HOW?
NEVER MIND HOW.
JUST BE SAFE.
I THINK HE LIKES ME.
AGUMON, DIGEVOLVE
TO GREYMON! GRAAH!
OH, NO! ANOTHER MONSTER!
DON'T WORRY.
THIS MONSTER'S ON OUR SIDE.
GET MY MON, GREYMON.
HURRY.
Phantomon: SHADOW SCYTHE!
WELL, GREYMON,
LOOKS LIKE YOUR TIME IS UP.
GET THE REST OF THE CROWD.
NO, STOP!
NOVABLAST!
SORRY, TAI, I'M LOSING.
WE'LL GET YOUR MOM LATER.
RIGHT NOW WE'VE GOT TO
GET OUT OF HERE.
Kari: MOMMY!
Tai: MOM, WE'LL BE BACK.
KARI! TAI!
WE'LL FOLLOW THEM
AND FIND OUT
WHERE THEY'VE TAKEN HER.
BUT WILL IT WORK?
WE'LL SEE.
SORA, IT'S YOU.
OH, NO, MIMI,
THEY GOT YOU, TOO?
PSST. I CAN
DIGEVOLVE ANYTIME.
JUST SAY THE WORD.
THERE'S TOO MANY PEOPLE,
AND TOO MANY OF THEM.
LET'S SEE HOW
THIS PLAYS OUT.
YOU'LL BE OUR TRUMP CARD
FOR LATER.
GOT IT.
I CAN'T STAND IT.
I CAN'T STAND NOT KNOWING.
HOW CAN I CALM DOWN?
FOR ALL WE KNOW,
THAT MONSTER'S DEVOURED
THE CHILDREN BY NOW.
DON'T WORRY.
HE'S ONE OF OURS.
THERE'S A LOT MORE
WHERE HE CAME FROM.
WE'VE GOT
SOME POWERFUL FRIENDS.
BESIDES, WE'VE GOT
TRUTH AND JUSTICE
AND ALL OF THAT GOOD STUFF
ON OUR SIDE.
IF YOU CAN'T BEAT THEM,
JOIN THEM.
NOW LET'S GO INSIDE
AND FIND SORA.
RIGHT!
WAIT.
THIS MAY BE
A STRANGE QUESTION,
BUT DID SORA EVER SAY --
DID SHE TELL YOU --
DOES SORA HATE ME?
WHAT? OH, BOY,
DO YOU HAVE IT WRONG.
Sora: I REALIZED
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU
THE WAY MY MOTHER
WORRIES ABOUT ME,
AND NOW I KNOW FOR SURE --
MY MOM LOVED ME ALL ALONG.
AND IT WAS YOUR LOVE
THAT HELPED ME
DIGEVOLVE, SORA.
I'M GLAD.
SORA...
HOW COULD IT BE WORSE?
YOU COULD WORK
IN A FOAM RUBBER SUIT
WITH KIDS KICKING YOU,
RIGHT, GUYS?
Monsters: RIGHT.
Mimi: WHAT IS IT, MOM?
I JUST CAN'T STAY
IN THIS PLACE
ONE SECOND LONGER.
YOU'VE BEEN WANTING
TO GET AWAY.
WHO ASKED YOU TO TALK?
I'M SORRY, CHILDREN.
I'M NOT USED
TO BEING HELD CAPTIVE
BY CREATURES
FROM ANOTHER WORLD.
Charlie: DON'T WORRY, LADY.
YOU'LL GET USED TO IT.
I DON'T WANT TO.
I WANT TO GO HOME,
SLEEP IN MY OWN BED,
LIVE LIFE TO THE FULLEST,
CLEAN LINT OUT OF MY DRYER,
PICK UP AFTER MY DOGGY.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING
ON MY SOAP OPERAS.
I'M SO GLAD I GOT THAT
OFF MY CHEST.
ENOUGH OF THIS.
WE NEED A PLAN.
YEAH, JEREMIAH.
WHY DON'T YOU HELP US
INSTEAD OF LISTENING
TO THOSE
MIND-OVER-MATTER TAPES?
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
THE ONLY WAY TO WEAKEN BAKKEMON
IS WITH MIND OVER MATTER.
HUH? MIND OVER WHAT?
IT'S AN OLD ROMAN TECHNIQUE.
REPEAT A PHRASE OVER AND OVER.
IT HELPS YOU FOCUS YOUR MIND.
WE NEED SOME OF YOU
TO ATTACK THE BAKKEMON
WHILE THE REST OF US
COME UP WITH
A MIND-OVER-MATTER CHANT.
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
JUST DO WHAT SHE SAYS,
ALL RIGHT?
HALF OF YOU COME WITH ME.
LET'S GET THEM!
[ SCREAMING ]
Woman: WOMEN AND CHILDREN,
FOLLOW ME!
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS.
BAKKEMON, LOSE YOUR POWER.
[ CROWD SCREAMING ]
WE MADE IT!
WE'RE SAFE AT LAST!
OOPS. SPOKE TOO SOON.
IT'S DARK TYRANNOMON.
HE WAS ACTUALLY
A NICE GUY ONCE.
HE WAS TAKEN OVER
BY AN EVIL COMPUTER VIRUS,
AND HIS PERSONALITY
DID A 180.
HUH? WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
YOU COULDN'T BE
IN SAFER HANDS!
DAD!
ALLEMON, DIGEVOLVE
TO TOGEMON!
BACK TO THE STONE AGE
WITH YOU!
DAD, DAD!
HONEY BUNCH,
ARE YOU OKAY?
I GUESS I MADE
A FOOL OF MYSELF, HUH?
MNH-MNH.
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
THAT WAS THE BRAVEST THING
I EVER SAW.
REALLY?
REALLY.
MEAN IT?
I MEAN IT.
OH, HONEY.
[ TALKING OVER EACH OTHER ]
AAH!
NO!
TOGEMON!
IT'S NO USE!
SAVE YOURSELF!
I GOT IT UNDER CONTROL.
NO PROBLEM.
OH, THIS IS THE END.
IT'S OVER.
MYOTISMON
WILL RULE THE WORLD.
OH!
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
NOW MY FAMILY'S GOING
TO SUFFER,
AND SO ARE MY FRIENDS.
THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOMETHING I CAN DO.
TOGEMON, DIGEVOLVE TO...
LILIMON!
NO!
Woman: WHERE'D SHE COME FROM?
FLOWER CANNON!
WHOA! WHO ARE YOU?
IT'S JUST LITTLE OLD ME,
OR, SHOULD I SAY,
LITTLE OLD US.
I'M PALMON
AND TOGEMON, TOO.
THIS IS JUST
MY FULLY DIGEVOLVED FORM.
YOU CAN CALL ME LILIMON.
AM I IN BAD TASTE?
NO WAY.
I'M SORRY
I EVER SAID THAT.
NO BIGGIE.
WHOOPSIE, YOU'LL HAVE TO
BE QUICKER THAN THAT.
BE CAREFUL!
YOUR WISH TO SAVE
YOUR FAMILY AND FRIENDS
BROUGHT ME
INTO EXISTENCE.
MIMI, YOU'RE A VERY
SPECIAL GIRL,
EVEN THOUGH YOUR WARDROBE
SOMETIMES CLASHES.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LATER.
RIGHT NOW I HAVE
A DINOSAUR TO TAME.
MOO!
MY FLOWER WREATH COUNTERACTED
THE EVIL COMPUTER VIRUS,
SO HE OUGHT TO BE
AS GENTLE AS A LAMB
FROM NOW ON.
NICE TYRANNOMON.
ATTA BOY.
Man: PLEASE BEAR WITH US.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
WHAT MADE ME THINK
THE BOATS WOULD BE RUNNING
WHEN NOTHING ELSE IS?
IT COULD BE WORSE.
PLEASE STOP SAYING
I HAVE NEWS FOR YOU.
IT IS WORSE.
THE WORLD IS IN TURMOIL,
AND WE'RE WAITING FOR A RIDE.
WE MIGHT AS WELL
JUST GIVE UP RIGHT NOW.
WELL, I WOULDN'T
GO THAT FAR.
AFTER ALL, IT COULD
BE WORSE. HUH?
[ Thinking ]
MAYBE IF I CAN JUST GET
TO THAT SATELLITE DISH.
YOU OKAY, AGUMON?
I'VE FELT BETTER.
TAI, UP HERE!
MATT, IS THAT YOU?
HEY, WE GOT TO TALK.
YOU FEEL ANY BETTER?
A LOT BETTER.
THANKS, KARI.
Matt: WHAT?
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
Tai: NO, IT'S TRUE.
KARI'S THE EIGHTH CHILD.
ENOUGH!
THAT NEW-AGE PSYCHOBABBLE
WON'T HELP YOU
WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
MY PRETTY LITTLE MISS.
SEIZE HERE! TAKE HER AWAY!
BOO!
WHAT?
BIYOMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
BIRDRAMON!
OH, IT'S JUST A BIRD --
A LARGE BIRD, I GRANT YOU.
A LARGE ANGRY BIRD. AAH!
SORA...
OH, MOM, I'M SO --
THERE'S NO TIME NOW,
HONEY.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET OUT
OF HERE. HURRY.
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU?
[ GROWLING ]
GET MOVING.
I'LL BE FINE.
NO, MOTHER!
WE WON!
WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
BACK TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
WITH YOU.
YOU ARE SUCH
A BAD SPORT.
YOU METTLESOME
LITTLE FLOWER CHILD.
IT'S TIME I PLUCKED
YOUR PETALS.
CRIMSON LIGHTNING!
Man: WILL LILIMON WITHSTAND
MYOTISMON'S CRIMSON LIGHTNING,
OR WILL MIMI LOSE
HER BEST FRIEND?
NEXT TIME ON "DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS."