NARRATOR:
DemiDevimon tricked Izzy
and made him fall into
Vademon's universe.
Convincing Izzy to
give up his curiosity,
Vademon turned him into
a total like zombie.
To make things worse,
that brainhead got hold
of his tag and crest.
Tentomon got so bummed out that
he De‐digivolved to Pabumon.
Thankfully, Izzy finally
snapped out of it
and with Pabumon's help,
got back the tag and crest.
Pabumon digivolved
to MegaKabuterimon
and sent Vademon clear
into another dimension.
Later, brainhead.
( electronic music )
♪ Digimon, Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters
Digimon are the champions ♪
♪ Change into
digital champions ♪
♪ To save the digital world ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters
Digimon are the champions ♪
♪ Digivolve into champion ♪
♪ Digivolve into ultimate ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters
Digimon are the champions ♪
♪ Digimon, digital
monsters, Digimon
AGUMON: Hey,
what's wrong you guys?
Can't you make this
bucket go any faster?
JOE: What are
you doing to help?
Watching for icebergs.
We'd gladly trade
places with you,
but unfortunately, our little
legs won't reach the pedals.
Hey, we could go faster
if we threw you off.
You wouldn't.
It's tempting.
GOMAMON: Better not.
JOE: Wow, that
palace is huge.
And way up there.
As if my legs weren't
tired already.
But there's no doubt about it.
That is Mimi, so up we go.
JOE: How do they
get their mail?
( voices chattering )
Is this a palace or
some kind of a loony bin?
Seems like it's both.
Her highness is getting angry.
GOMAMON: These are Gekomon?
I've heard of them,
they really love music.
Not surprising, since they're
born with those horns.
Hurry, before
she blows her top.
AGUMON: And I've heard
of the other Digimon.
They're called Otamamon.
Hurry, hurry.
Can you help us?
We're looking for someone.
About time you got here.
Where's the triple
hot fudge sundae
we ordered for delivery
to the princess?
GROUP: That's not us.
GEKOMON: Then you must be
delivering her bacon chili
cheeseburger with fries and
a super‐sized milkshake.
GROUP: That's not us either.
Of course not.
They're delivering
the garden fresh salad
with low‐fat dressing
without dessert.
GROUP: We'd like to ask
a question if you don't mind.
Her Highness asked
for a fudge sundae.
No, she wants
a bacon chili cheeseburger.
Excuse me, she said
she wanted a green salad.
Hey, excuse me.
Have you seen a girl in a hat?
OTAMAMON: Hey, we're
ordering lunch here.
Well, then I'll have a burger.
All the princess
really cares about
is that polka dot party
dress she ordered.
Old news, now she
wants pink leather pants
with matching boots
and accessories.
No one told me that.
Get with the program.
( Digimon arguing )
It sounds to me like
this princess of theirs
is extremely picky.
She sounds kinda
spoiled, if you ask me.
I wonder what happens if
they don't do what she says.
DIGIMON: Here she comes.
GEKOMON: Presenting
her highness, the princess.
TAI: Cool, we're gonna
get to meet the princess.
Huh, it's Mimi.
Oh, bummer. (sighs)
Huh.
What a surprise.
You're telling me.
What are you doing up there?
What do you think?
I'm being a princess,
of course.
So you're the spoiled princess
we've been hearing about.
GROUP: We should've
known it was Mimi.
Don't call me Mimi anymore.
That's Princess, now.
DEMIDEVIMON: Don't you
worry, your mighty wickedness.
This time, we cannot fail.
GHOSTLY VOICE: We?
You'd better not fail.
It's in the bag,
piece of cake.
GHOSTLY VOICE: Is the
plan at the palace working?
Couldn't be better.
The Gekomon are spoiling her
rotten and she's eating it up.
If she keeps this
up much longer,
her Crest of Sincerity's
gonna be useless, master.
GHOSTLY VOICE: Do you
know what will happen
if you disappoint me
again, DemiDevimon?
I got a vague idea.
GHOSTLY VOICE: Good,
then see that you don't.
JOE: Well, the important
thing is that you're alright.
Yeah, that's for sure.
Well, come on,
let's get a move on.
No way.
Right, you wanna
change first, we'll wait.
For what? I'm
keeping this dress on.
And it's beautiful,
but it's not the best thing to
wear to walk long distances.
Walking? I have no
intention of walking anywhere.
Are you expecting us
to carry you out of
here, your majesty?
No, I'm not going.
GROUP: Huh?
Why would I leave?
I am a princess here.
Besides, who knows if we'll
ever find our way home,
so I might as well live
large and in charge.
You must be kidding.
No way, take a look around.
I've got a nice bed,
pretty clothes, food.
It's like having
a birthday every day.
I am a princess.
And you want me to give this up?
I don't think so.
PALMON: Is something wrong?
Another servant?
GOMAMON: No, it's Palmon.
JOE: Finally,
a voice of reason.
Palmon, come talk
some sense into Mimi.
As in princess?
Oh, no, not you too.
Okay, that's enough.
This is no time
for playing games.
Both of you change out
of those dumb clothes
and let's get out of here.
I am not playing a game, Tai.
I'm staying, you can go anytime.
Why don't you guys go
look for the others?
Begone from my palace.
Wait, Mimi, don't be
mean, they're our friends.
If you wanna go, be my guest.
You are coming with us.
Get down off that
high horse of yours
and shift your rear
into high gear.
Yeah, come on,
why do you think
we almost killed ourselves
trying to find you?
'Cause you are part of the team.
That's very nice,
but I am not going.
That's it, Mimi.
Like it or not, Joe's right.
We've gotta stick together so
I'm not budging from this spot
until you come to your
senses and leave with us.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Right.
Really? You all
keep forgetting
who's in charge around
here. (bell ringing)
Your Highness, what
is it that you desire?
I desire these rude
and bothersome peasants
to be removed from
my boudoir at once.
GEKOMON: Yes, Princess.
( all arguing )
Oh, Mimi.
TAI: I won't dissect
frogs in biology, okay?
If that's the way
you treat your guests,
we're never coming back.
Now what are we gonna do?
She's totally into
this digi‐fairy tale.
I wonder what she
could've done to get them
to wait on her hand
and foot like this.
GEKOMON: You
really wanna know?
TAI: Sure.
JOE: You're not taking us
to an evil Digimon, are you?
TAI: What if Mimi catches us?
She won't.
Here's our master,
Lord Shogunmon.
TAI: Whoa, somebody's
had a few too many donuts.
JOE: Is it a statue or what?
No, it's not a statue,
he's very much alive.
He may be alive, but
he's not lively, is he?
He's sleeping.
He's been this way
for over 300 years.
You see, Lord Shogunmon
was proud of his voice
and entered this singing
contest, but he lost.
He felt so bad, he
fell into a deep sleep
from which he's never recovered.
It's said only
a voice as beautiful
as the one that beat
him can wake him.
For centuries we've tried,
but every song's failed.
We Gekomon love music but
unfortunately, not one of us
has a voice that would
be considered beautiful.
Then we got a break.
A strange little Digimon spoke
of a girl with a pretty voice.
He told us where to
find her and we did.
♪ I wanna sing a song ♪
♪ A song that'll wake you up ♪
♪ And when you hear my voice ♪
♪ you'll call me
A sweet buttercup ♪
♪ Just give me a listen ♪
Sorry, I forgot the words.
Wow, you mean all
this is for me?
Maybe this will help
you remember the words.
♪ I wanna sing a song ♪
♪ A song that'll wake you up ♪
♪ When you hear my
Voice, you'll call me ♪
You know, this
place is too dark.
How about we get a disco ball
and some spotlights, huh?
And of course, we'll need
hair, makeup and costumes.
( Digimon cheering )
I'm tired, let's
pick it up tomorrow.
And that's the way it's been.
One excuse after another.
We've done all she's wanted.
We've even redecorated
the entire palace for her.
I used to like pink, but now
I can't stand to look at it.
And if any one of
us complains to her.
Whoa, be careful,
you wouldn't want me
to lose my voice now, would you?
So we're in a terrible
position, you see?
We're totally helpless.
Unfortunately, you've
given Mimi the life
she's been accustomed
to and then some.
Well, since your
friends of hers.
Could you please
reason with her, please?
We'd be so eternally grateful.
I don't think she
knows what reason is.
TAI: Just leave it to
me, guys, I've got it.
GROUP: Huh?
I knew it, I knew
you'd come through.
Yay.
What are you thinking, Tai?
Well, who says you need
Mimi to wake up Jumbo?
Crank it up
and let me take a shot.
ALL: You? ( laughing )
TAI: What're you laughing at?
(upbeat pop music)
♪ I'm gonna sing a song ♪
♪ A song that will wake you up ♪
♪ I'm gonna belt it out ♪
♪ Shogunmon is gonna get up ♪
Hey, wake up.
Hey, let me give it a shot.
♪ I'm attempting to sing
A song ♪
♪ A song that'll awaken
You and aid all the Gekomon ♪
♪ that are loyal
To your world view ♪
♪ and the idea of
You being in charge ♪
♪ I'm attempting to sing
A song ♪
♪ A song that'll awaken
you and aid all the Gekomon ♪
♪ I croon this song to you,
a tune from now until June ♪
♪ When you hear us singing ♪
♪ You'll call us
singing foghorns ♪
♪ We just wanna wake you up ♪
♪ So don't close your ears ♪
♪ Or you can sleep for years ♪
TAI: It's no use.
After that, he might not wake
up for another 300 years.
‐ Hey, guys.
‐ Palmon.
Why did you all
disappear like that?
It's like you weren't
even happy to see us.
What're you talking about?
In case you hadn't
noticed, Mimi's gone nuts.
Yeah?
Hmm.
Now that I think of it,
she has kind of gone
off the deep end.
I mean, even for her.
Oh, you noticed?
You're so observant.
So she'll be performing
and won't even know it.
Yeah, and we'll get
the whole thing on tape.
Watch it.
What's this?
PALMON: It's a karaoke set.
Yes, I can see that.
But what's it doing
in my royal chambers?
I just love hearing you sing.
I thought you might give
us a private concert.
Here.
Thanks, you're the greatest.
Now, feel the music,
feel the music.
JOE: Tai, is
she falling for it?
Mhmm.
(Mimi humming)
What's that cord for?
I see.
(screams)
So you thought you
could pull a fast one
on Princess Mimi, did you?
‐ That's Princess Meanie.
‐ Yeah.
Who do you think
you are, anyway?
Don't you remember
we're your friends?
I remember you
tried to trick me.
We tried to trick you because
we're trying to save you.
Have you completely forgotten
about the Crest of Sincerity?
Have you completely
forgotten it's not nice
to lock people up
in your dungeon?
Where's your manners?
Wait.
Before you go, I have
something I wanna tell you.
Nobody likes you more than I do.
It hurts me deeply
to have to say this,
but you're a spoiled brat.
( gasps )
Is that a fact?
Well, it's nice to know
how you really feel.
FEMALE VOICE: What can I do?
( monsters growling )
( terrified gasp )
Hurry, stop them.
I've got to have your help.
DIGIMON: Sorry.
( gasps )
Oh, yeah, well, then
I won't sing anymore.
Big deal.
You didn't sing even when
we did what you wanted.
You're on your own.
Wait, don't leave me.
I'll sing for you, I promise.
Help me, please.
Sorry, but we only
help our friends.
What's wrong, Mimi?
What's the matter?
I thought you were having
the time of your life.
Palmon.
I've gotta go
now, Mimi, goodbye.
(Mimi screams)
Won't anybody help me? Please,
Palmon, don't leave me.
Hey, hey, hey, Mimi.
Where am I? What?
Do you have any idea
what that horrible dream
was trying to tell you, Mimi?
I'm sorry, oh, I really am.
Well, then you know
what you have to do
to make things right.
Yes.
That a girl, I knew
you'd find yourself again.
The crest.
Sora?
( snoring )
GEKOMON: Alright, wake up.
TAI: What now?
GEKOMON: The
princess wants you.
TAI: Is she gonna
chop off our heads?
JOE: Don't even joke.
OTAMAMON: What's going on?
GROUP: What's she up to?
First of all,
there's something
I have to say to everyone here.
Tai and Joe, Agumon
and Gomamon, Palmon,
all of you've been so
nice, I'm so sorry.
( all chattering )
I've been such a little idiot.
If you can find it in
your hearts to forgive me,
and I don't know why you
would, but if you can,
then I'd be honored to
sing for you one more time.
We forgive you.
Of course we do,
sing, Your Highness.
Thank you.
Hit the lights
and cue the music.
♪ I wanna sing a song ♪
♪ A song to bring
Shogunmon around ♪
♪ When he hears my voice ♪
♪ I hope he likes the sound ♪
♪ He has to listen ♪
♪ Listen to my sincere heart ♪
♪ I've learned my
Friends are friends ♪
♪ Even when they're apart ♪
♪ I've asked my
Friends to forgive me ♪
♪ from the bottom of my heart ♪
♪ If it's my choice
His eyes will open wide ♪
♪ And the Gekomon will be
Cheering, cheering with pride ♪
( crowd chattering )
GEKOMON: Don't panic, it's
our lord and master Shogunmon,
finally restored to us
after so many centuries.
I was having
such a nice sleep.
Which one of you
clowns woke me up?
Or should I just
squish all of you?
GEKOMON: Women
and Gekomon first!
( all yelling )
JOE: And I thought I was
cranky when I first wake up.
GOMAMON: Give me the
mean Mimi back any day.
GEKOMON: Whose idea was this?
Remind me never to
listen to them again.
You wanna hear some singing?
♪ The ground will shake when
You hear the noise I make ♪
♪ Because I'm glad
To be awake, yeah ♪
(screaming)
Mimi!
( electronic music )
♪ Digimon, digital monsters
Digimon are the champions ♪
PALMON: Palmon
Digivolve to...
Togemon!
That was a close one.
Can you forgive me?
Of course, I can.
Togemon, you're
the best, oh thank you.
I'm just glad old Mimi's back.
Really, you mean it?
Then let's take care of
this out of tune goon.
Hey, you, how about
some gratitude?
I sang you out of your 300
year nap, you wannabe crooner.
All that racket, it was you?
MIMI: Uh oh.
Oh, have you come to play?
GREYMON: Nova Blast.
IKKAKUMON: Harpoon Torpedo.
Now, it's showtime.
♪ Now why'd you try that
'cause I'll knock you flat ♪
♪ And now you're gonna feel it ♪
Did you see that?
Yeah, he gives new meaning
to the term flat note.
Watch out below!
(electronic music)
♪ Digimon, digital monsters
Digimon are the champions ♪
GREYMON: Greymon Digivolve to...
MetalGreymon.
♪ Digimon, digital monsters
Digimon are the champions ♪
♪ Digivolve into ultimate ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters
Digimon ♪
Yeah, give it to
him, MetalGreymon.
Giga Blaster!
He deserved to hear that last
flat note, don't you think?
(all laughing)
TAI: Well, ready to go, Mimi.
MIMI: Yeah, do you
think I could take
some of my princess
clothes with me?
TAI: Mimi.
MIMI: Well, it just
seems such a waste.
The jewels, at least?
GHOSTLY VOICE: Didn't you say
you knew what would
happen if you failed?
Well, when I said I
knew, I didn't really mean
that I knew knew,
you know what I mean?
But now that I do know, if
it's not too much trouble, sir,
could I bother you
for a glass of water?
( upbeat music )
( electronic music )