Sora: MYOTISMON CUT OFF ACCESS
IN AND OUT OF TOWN
TO FIND THE EIGHTH CHILD.
I WAS BEING HELD CAPTIVE
WITH OTHER PEOPLE
BY THE BAKIMON.
TO DISTRACT THEM,
I REPEATED THE CHANT
JOE HAD USED TO MAKE
THE BAKIMON LOSE THEIR POWER.
THAT WORKED
UNTIL PHANTOMON GOT WISE
AND DESTROYED MY RECORDING.
THEN DARK TYRANNIMON
SHOWED UP.
LITTLE PALMON
TURNED OVER A NEW LEAF
BY DIGEVOLVING
TO THE ULTIMATE LEVEL --
LILLYMON.
SHE WAS ABLE TO RETURN HIM
TO A TAME STATE.
THEN JUST TO MAKE THINGS
EVEN WORSE, MYOTISMON ARRIVED.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
FLOWER CANNON!
HA HA!
DO YOU EXPECT TO BEAT ME
WITH GERANIUMS?
MM!
NIGHTMARE CLAW!
OH. AAH!
LILLYMON!
GET OUT OF HERE,
SORA -- NOW.
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU, MOM?
JUST GO!
OH.
GRIZZLY WING!
[ BATS SQUEAK ]
[ PANTING ]
OHH!
OH, NO,
THEY'RE GOING TO GET HER!
AAH!
METEOR WING!
[ BATS SQUEAK ]
[ BIRDRAMON SHRIEKS ]
SORA, GET OUT,
HE'S WAY TOO STRONG.
SHE'S RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
GET AWAY YOU --
YOU THINGS! OH!
SORA, GO!
AAH!
I'LL COME BACK JUST AS SOON
AS I FIND THE OTHERS.
DON'T WORRY, MOM.
LET ME GO! LET ME GO!
POOR AGUMON. YOU'RE ALWAYS
GETTING BEAT UP.
THERE.
HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
YOU'RE GETTING
GOOD AT THIS.
Tai: NO WAY!
WAY! IT'S TRUE.
I SAW THE WHOLE THING.
THAT CREEPAZOID.
HE'S CUT OFF
THE WHOLE ENTIRE DISTRICT.
MM-HMM. IT'S THAT CRAZY
FOG BANK OF HIS.
THIS IS INSANE.
HOLDING THOUSANDS
OF PEOPLE PRISONER
JUST SO HE CAN FIND
THE EIGHTH CHILD.
AND THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT HE'LL DO
IF HE DOESN'T FIND HER.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT,
ISN'T IT?
IT'S ALL HAPPENING
BECAUSE HE'S LOOKING
FOR ME, RIGHT?
THAT'S WHY MOM AND DAD
AND EVERYBODY ARE --
NOW, DON'T SAY THAT.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
IT'S JUST
THE WAY THINGS ARE.
IT'S CALLED DESTINY.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
I'M GOING TO BRING
MOM AND DAD HOME
SAFE AND SOUND,
AND YOUR LITTLE BUDDY
GATOMON, TOO.
HEY, MATT,
DO ME A FAVOR
AND LOOK AFTER HER
TILL I GET BACK.
SURE, NO PROBLEM.
KARI, I NEED YOU TO BE
A BIG STRONG GIRL FOR ME
WHILE I'M AWAY.
OKAY.
PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
HEY, AREN'T I ALWAYS?
OKAY, IT'S 7:30.
GIVE ME 2 HOURS.
IF WE DON'T MAKE IT
BACK BY THEN,
YOU GUYS GET OUT OF HERE.
LET'S GO, AGUMON.
BE CAREFUL, MAN.
SEE YOU SOON.
EVERYTHING'S GOING
TO BE ALL RIGHT.
Agumon: WHOA!
I HOPE SO.
[ SIGHS ]
LOOK, E-MAIL FROM GENNAI.
Greetings!
Salutations from cyberspace...
GET TO THE POINT.
but this is no time
for pleasantries.
You're in a tight spot, eh?
The first thing to do
is put up a digital barrier.
A DIGITAL WHAT?
You're probably wondering
what that is.
Well, download the program,
and I'll explain.
If you can put it up in time,
the digital barrier
will protect you.
[ BAKIMON LAUGHING ]
Man: OH! OH!
THE BAKIMON ARE GETTING
CLOSER EVERY SECOND.
CAN'T YOU GO
ANY FASTER, IZZY?
I'M TRYING.
I TOLD DAD
I NEED A QUICKER MODEM.
Man: WHAT'S ALL
THE COMMOTION?
Man #2: THEY DON'T TELL YOU
ANYTHING THAT'S GOING ON.
WE'RE SORRY, BUT BECAUSE
OF FOG CONDITIONS,
NO FERRIES WILL BE
RUNNING TO THE DISTRICT
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE.
WHAT DO WE DO
IN THE MEANTIME?
PLEASE BEAR WITH US.
WE'RE DOING
EVERYTHING WE CAN.
YOU JUST HAVE TO WAIT
FOR THE FOG TO LIFT.
I'M GETTING A BAD FEELING
FROM THIS CROWD.
I THINK MAYBE
WE SHOULD BE GOING, T.K.
WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST I DO?
MY FAMILY'S IN THERE.
Woman: MINE TOO!
PLEASE, STAY CALM.
IN CASES OF EMERGENCY,
YOU MIGHT TRY RENTING
A PRIVATE BOAT
DOWN AT THE HARBOR.
MOMMY?
T.K., WHERE ARE YOU? AAH!
MOMMY!
[ BAKIMON LAUGH ]
[ SCREAMING ]
COME OUT, COME OUT,
WHEREVER YOU ARE.
Man: NO!
COME ON, COME ON.
IT IS TIME TO GO, IZZY.
WE'VE GOT
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
NO, BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
WE'LL BE SAFER HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, IZZY?
TRUST ME,
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
JUST GIVE ME ANOTHER
COUPLE OF MINUTES HERE.
NO, YOU ARE COMING NOW.
WAIT, MOM. LET ME GO!
[ BAKIMON LAUGH ]
MOM, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
NO, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THIS ISN'T THE TIME.
NOW, WILL YOU PLEASE LEAVE
THAT COMPUTER ALONE?
DEAR, MAYBE HE KNOWS
WHAT HE'S DOING.
LET'S TRUST THE BOY,
ALL RIGHT?
THE KIDS SEEM TO KNOW
MORE ABOUT IT THAN WE DO.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
GO FOR IT, SON.
NEXT.
TRICK OR TREAT?
DONE.
DIGITAL BARRIER
COMING ON NOW!
AAH!
[ BAKIMON LAUGH ]
HMM?
HUH?
THAT'S FUNNY,
I COULD HAVE SWORN -- HUH.
THERE'S NO ONE HERE.
LET'S GET MOVING.
OHH.
IT WORKED.
THE DIGITAL BARRIER
IS IN PLACE.
HUH? AAH!
OOPS.
WELL, NOW THAT YOU KNOW
I CAN TALK,
MY NAME'S TENTOMON.
PLEASED TO MAKE
YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
Man: ARE THEY
KEEPING US HERE FOREVER?
Woman: THEY'RE JUST
KEEPING US HERE.
I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO WITH US?
NOW WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN?
IF I TOLD YOU NOW,
IT WOULD JUST SIMPLY
RUIN THE SURPRISE
THAT'S COMING UP.
IN THE MEANTIME,
WHY DOESN'T EVERYBODY
TAKE A LITTLE NAP?
[ SIGHING AND SNORING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ BAKIMON LAUGH ]
IT'S NOT HER.
NEXT.
Bakimon: OKAY, NEXT.
BEWARE, GATOMON.
AH.
[ GASPS ]
IF YOU LIE TO ME,
I WILL SIMPLY
DESTROY THEM ALL.
[ CRIES ]
[ CROWD GRUMBLES ]
Man: HEY! SLOW DOWN!
[ PANTS ]
I THOUGHT WE WERE GOING
TO BE GONERS.
JOE!
HEY, T.K.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE
IN TOWN WITH THE OTHERS.
NO, I WAS ACROSS THE HARBOR
WHEN THE POWER WENT OUT.
HMM?
SO, WE'RE BOTH
STUCK OUT HERE
WHILE EVERYONE ELSE
IS IN THERE.
YEAH. WHO KNOWS WHAT
MYOTISMON'S PLANNING TO DO
INSIDE THAT EVIL
BLANKET OF FOG.
NOT SO GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH TALK.
IT'S TIME FOR ACTION.
WE'VE GOT TO GET THERE.
I KNOW. WHAT WILL WE USE
TO GET ACROSS?
THIS IS WHAT.
THE ANSWER'S RIGHT HERE.
GOMAMON.
AH, FRESH AIR.
[ LAUGHS ]
ARE YOU READY
TO GIVE IT A TRY?
SURE, IF YOU ARE.
T.K.! T.K.!
GOMAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
IKKAKUMON.
ALL ABOARD.
LOOK, IT'S ANOTHER ONE.
Woman: WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
OH, T.K.
UH-OH.
T.K., WHAT IS THAT THING?
GET DOWN FROM THERE.
OH, IT'S OKAY MOM.
BY THE WAY, THIS IS
A FRIEND OF MINE.
HIS NAME'S JOE.
IT'S VERY NICE
TO MEET YOU, MA'AM.
I WAS IN T.K.'S
WOODWORKING CLASS
AT SUMMER CAMP.
HE NEARLY CUT OFF
ONE OF MY FINGERS.
PLEASE, STOP.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THE SAW SLIPPED, BUT I
MISSED HIM BY A MILE.
THAT'S NOT
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
SO LONG, MOM.
BE BACK WITH MATT AND DAD
BY DINNERTIME.
OH, NO.
I'VE LOST ALL OF THEM NOW.
Gennai: So, Izzy, if you're
still listening to me,
that means the digital barrier
must have worked.
Izzy: LIKE A CHARM.
The fog barrier surrounding
the entire district
is not a natural phenomenon.
It's Myotismon's doing.
WELL, DUH.
YEAH, BUT WHAT
DO WE DO ABOUT IT?
You're probably wondering
when I'm going to tell you
what you can do about it.
The source of the fog is here.
Attack its source
to bring down the barrier.
THAT'S A TV STATION.
LET'S GET MOVING.
AYE, AYE.
THEY MIGHT COME BACK.
THE SAFEST THING
YOU GUYS CAN DO
IS TO STAY
RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE.
IN HERE, THE DIGITAL BARRIER
WILL PROTECT YOU.
I'LL BE BACK AS SOON
AS I CAN. SO LONG.
Mother: WAIT!
YOU'VE GROWN
SO MUCH, IZZY,
AND IT'S OBVIOUS YOU CAN
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF,
BUT YOU WILL ALWAYS BE
MY LITTLE BOY.
SO, PLEASE, SON,
BE CAREFUL.
I WILL. DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ME, MOM.
I'LL MAKE SURE HE'S SAFE.
[ SOBS ]
NEVER A MOMENT'S REST.
IT'S ALWAYS "SEIZE HER"
OR "GRAB HIM"
OR "GO TERRORIZE
THAT OLD LADY."
I AM ONE POOPED SPOOK.
YEAH!
OKAY, START TALKING.
WHERE ARE YOU KEEPING EVERYONE,
YOU LITTLE CREEP?
HEY, TAI.
SORA!
SO, YOU'RE ALL RIGHT?
HEY, COME BACK.
THE CONVENTION CENTER --
MYOTISMON'S HOLDING THEM
PRISONER THERE.
EVERYONE
IN THE WHOLE DISTRICT?
YEAH, INCLUDING MIMI.
HE'S GOT YOUR PARENTS
AS WELL.
[ GASPS ]
I'VE ABOUT HAD IT
WITH THIS GUY.
OKAY, SORA,
YOU GO HOOK UP WITH MATT.
HE'S IN THE WAREHOUSE
BY AQUA CITY.
HMM. I'M ON MY WAY.
LET'S GO.
Sora: AQUA CITY, BIRDRAMON.
STEP ON IT!
[ LAUGHS ]
THE PLOT THICKENS.
THE SATELLITE DISH
WON'T RESPOND. RATS!
COME ON, THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOME WAY OF COMMUNICATING
WITH THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
[ PANTS ]
WHOA! I HAD NO IDEA
TV STATIONS WERE SO BIG.
IF I'M GOING TO DESTROY IT,
I SHOULD DIGEVOLVE.
HOLD ON FOR A MINUTE.
FOR ALL WE KNOW,
THERE MIGHT STILL BE
SOME PEOPLE INSIDE.
WE BETTER CHECK IT OUT.
[ CHILDREN CRYING ]
[ Thinking ]
HANG IN THERE, MIMI.
I'LL GET ALL OF YOU OUT.
I PROMISED KARI.
Matt: WIZARDMON, HUH?
IS THAT
YOUR DIGIMON'S NAME?
Kari: NO, MINE IS GATOMON.
WIZARDMON IS LIKE
HER BEST FRIEND,
BUT HE'S GONE NOW.
HE GOT CAPTURED
BY THE BAD DIGIMON.
IT MUST BE AWFUL
LOSING YOUR BEST FRIEND.
MY MOMMY GOT CAPTURED
BY THEM, TOO,
BUT NOT MY DADDY.
DO YOU THINK MAYBE
MY DADDY GOT AWAY?
HE'S ALL RIGHT,
DON'T YOU THINK?
AND MOMMY WILL BE, TOO,
'CAUSE TAI'S GOING
TO RESCUE HER, RIGHT?
SURE HE WILL, KARI,
BUT LET'S REMEMBER,
TAI'S JUST ONE KID,
AND HE'S FIGHTING HUNDREDS.
[ Crying ] I WANT MOMMY
TO COME BACK.
NICE WORK.
HAVE SOME COMPASSION.
CAN'T YOU SEE SHE'S WORRIED
ABOUT HER FAMILY?
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT YOURS,
AREN'T YOU?
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
ONCE WE GET
PAST THE BRIDGE
WE'LL BE THROUGH
THE BARRIER.
T.K.: RIGHT.
[ MONSTER GROWLS ]
IS YOUR TUMMY RUMBLING,
OR DID I HEAR SOMETHING?
HUH? LIKE WHAT?
WAIT, WHAT'S UP THERE
BY THE BRIDGE?
[ GROWLS ]
I KNEW THIS WAS TOO EASY.
THAT'S MEGASEADRAMON.
THE REGULAR OLD SEADRAMON
WAS BAD ENOUGH,
BUT COMPARED TO THIS
FULLY DIGEVOLVED VERSION,
IT WAS JUST AN ANGRY GUPPY.
[ ROARING ]
Both: AAH!
[ SNARLING ]
OH, GREAT, WE'LL PROBABLY
GET BLAMED FOR THIS.
Ikkakumon: HARPOON TORPEDO!
[ GROWLS ]
BULL'S-EYE!
RIGHT ON THE BUTTON.
[ ROARS ]
THUNDER JAVELIN!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
AAH!
T.K.? JOE? T.K.?
HELP ME!
I CAN'T SWIM SO GOOD,
PATAMON.
[ STRUGGLES ]
OH, NO.
[ Thinking ] MATT, BROTHER,
I NEED YOU.
WHAT WAS THAT?
GRAB ON!
JOE.
JUST HANG ON TIGHT
TO THAT,
AND YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
I WOULDN'T WANT YOUR MOM
TO WORRY ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE JUST A KID.
I'M RESPONSIBLE FOR YOU.
T.K.: JOE? JOE!
IKKAKUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
ZUDOMON.
T.K.: WHOA!
WHO'S THAT, PATAMON?
Patamon: DON'T WORRY,
HE'S ONE OF OURS.
THAT'S ZUDOMON.
HE'S THE FULLY DIGEVOLVED
VERSION OF IKKAKUMON.
I WAS WONDERING
WHEN HE'D FINALLY SHOW UP.
[ GROWLS ]
JOE! HUH? OH.
Joe: HE'S CUTTING AN OPENING
IN THE FOG BANK.
THUNDER JAVELIN!
I DON'T THINK SO.
YIPPEE!
THAT'S MY DIGIMON.
VULCAN'S HAMMER!
[ ROARS ]
OHH. AAH!
[ GROANS ]
WAY TO GO!
WE BETTER GET GOING
BEFORE THE FOG BANK
CLOSES AGAIN.
YOU'VE GOT A POINT.
ENGINES AHEAD FULL,
ZUDOMON.
OKAY,
KEEP YOUR EYES PEELED.
NOW, IF I WERE
A FOG BARRIER GENERATOR,
WHERE WOULD I BE?
GET BACK!
BACK UP. WE'LL GO
THE OTHER WAY.
UH-OH.
NOT THAT WAY, EITHER.
THEY'VE GOT US
SURROUNDED.
WHOA!
[ BAKIMON LAUGH ]
KEEP QUIET.
BORING, HUH?
YOU SAID IT.
[ GASPS ]
WHO ARE YOU?
T.K.: I CAN'T SEE
ANYTHING IN HERE.
I JUST HOPE
WE DON'T END UP GOING
IN THE TOTALLY
WRONG DIRECTION.
Voice: TAKE ME
TO GATOMON, PLEASE.
HUH? WHO'S THERE?
I'M WIZARDMON.
MUST FIND GATOMON.
IMPORTANT.
NOT SO FAST THERE.
AREN'T YOU ONE
OF MYOTISMON'S HENCHMEN?
HE LOOKS BEAT UP
PRETTY BAD.
GOT TO GIVE GATOMON THIS.
LOOK, HE'S GOT
SOMEBODY'S CREST.
YES, IT BELONGS
TO THE EIGHTH CHILD. OHH.
T.K. and Joe:
OH, THE EIGHTH CHILD!
HMM.
YOUR BROTHER SHOULD HAVE
BEEN BACK BY NOW.
WHERE IS HE?
HEY, IS ANYBODY THERE?
SORA! WHAT'S UP?
MATT, THANK GOODNESS.
MYOTISMON'S ROUNDED UP
THE WHOLE DISTRICT.
HE'S HOLDING EVERYBODY
AT THE CONVENTION CENTER.
SO, WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
Phantomon:
I HAVE A SUGGESTION.
YOU SEE,
I'VE NEVER UNDERSTOOD
WHY THE MASTER IS WASTING
ALL THIS TIME
SEARCHING
FOR THE EIGHTH CHILD
WHEN IT WOULD BE SO MUCH EASIER
JUST TO DESTROY YOU ALL.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ ROARS ]
Phantomon: SAY HELLO
TO TUSKMON, AND WATCH OUT --
AVOIDING HIS RAZOR-SHARP HORNS
IS NO EASY TUSK.
HA HA. SORRY.
AND HERE'S THE SECOND MEMBER
OF OUR TAG TEAM.
AAH!
SNIMON -- A DEADLY
PRAYING MANTIS DIGIMON,
WHICH IS SO APPROPRIATE
BECAUSE YOU'RE ALL ABOUT
TO BECOME HIS PREY.
Sora: WATCH OUT!
Matt: GABUMON!
GABUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GARURUMON.
[ ROARS ]
Birdramon: DON'T WORRY.
WE CAN TAKE THESE GUYS.
[ MONSTERS GROWL ]
TIN SICKLES!
[ GROWLS ]
HEY, YOU'RE GOING
THE WRONG WAY!
[ GROANS ]
SHADOW SCYTHE.
GET BACK! AHH!
[ MOANS ]
BIRDRAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GARUDAMON.
TIN SICKLES!
OHH.
AAH!
Phantomon: KIND OF
CHOKES YOU UP, DOESN'T IT?
NO!
STOP IT NOW!
THAT'S ENOUGH!
WHAT'S IT DOING?
IT'S ME YOU WANT.
I'M THE EIGHTH CHILD.
IF YOU'LL JUST STOP
HURTING MY FRIENDS,
I'LL COME WITH YOU QUIETLY
WHEREVER YOU WANT.
WHAT A REFRESHINGLY
HELPFUL ATTITUDE.
IT'S A DEAL.
[ GROWLS ]
[ GASPS ]
I'M READY.
HURRY, MATT! STOP HER!
NO, KARI!
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING!
KARI!
Sora: OH, NO, MATT.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
TAI IS GOING
TO BE SO MAD AT ME.
WILL THE DIGI-DESTINED
FIND KARI
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS."