[grumbles]
You evil, frazzling meanie!
I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
A "frazzling meanie"?
Yeah, that's right!
And, if you know what's good for
you, you'll tell me who you are!
Um. My name is Ayumu Miho.
Who are you?
[SANA]
Uh...
Ha! I'm Sana Kashimura!
And I'm amazing.
Where are we?
How did you bring us here?
I don't think you're ready
to hear the answer,
but I'll tell you anyway.
This... is Wonderland!
I opened a door here
so I could catch you.
Everything that happens here,
happens because I want it to.
In Wonderland, I do whatever
I want, and no one can beat me.
Did you create this place
using your magic?
You be quiet.
That's enough questions.
I've got you now, and I'm
not letting you leave here
until you apologize. Understand?
I don't care if you cry,
or if you get hungry.
And no potty breaks!
[gasps]
Okay. Stay here and think
about what you've done!
[AYUMU grunting]
[gasping]
Please listen to me!
[SANA]
What are you doing?
Let go! I told you to stay here!
[AYUMU] Hold on!
I'll apologize, I really will.
Just give me a chance!
I don't care about that!
Now let go of the door!
I mean it, though! I'm sorry!
You don't know how hard
I've been trying to find you!
[gasps]
[AYUMU]
I think you can help me.
You obviously know something
about this weird power.
Please!
She's my best friend, and
she's putting herself through
terrible pain because she
thinks there's no other way!
[gasps]
[AYUMU gasps]
What are you doing?
[AYUMU screams]
[train whistles]
[gasping]
[screams]
[AYUMU gasping]
[SANA grunting]
[SANA]
Ugh, darn it, darn it, darn it!
I've got that
frazzled feeling again!
It's your fault because you had
to open your big, dumb mouth
and say stuff instead
of just shutting up!
Yonaga and Asahi were worried
about that stupid friend
of yours, too, and
I don't know why!
It's not right!
I have this weird feeling
I can't understand.
It won't stop!
Well, we could talk about it.
[SANA]
Shut up!
Ugh! I don't wanna talk to you!
When you talk, I get confused,
and that makes me angry!
Really, really angry!
I know. I'm sorry.
I mean it.
[SANA] I thought
I told you to shut up!
I don't want to hear it!
Quit apologizing already!
It's driving me crazy!
[AYUMU]
B-But why?
It's what you asked for.
I just want you to forgive me--
Well, it's not gonna happen!
Now just shut up! Shut up!
Shut up, shut up,
shut up, shut up--
Uh?
Uh. Uh-oh. He's calling.
I need to hide you for now.
[AYUMU]
Hey! Hold on!
You better stay quiet! Or else!
[SANA whimpers]
Okay. What are you up to?
And what did you
do to my bathroom?
[SANA]
I, uh...
This is one weird bathroom.
[ZOROKU grunts]
[SANA]
Ow!
[ZOROKU] Don't even think
about running away from me.
What's going on here?
Explain yourself.
[SANA]
...Ow! Ow!
[AYUMU gasps]
Huh?!
I'll take your order
whenever you're ready.
[AYUMU]
Huh?
[SHOP WORKER A]
Thanks, have a nice day!
[SANA]
Hey!
Turn around. Over here!
Don't recognize me?
Is that you, Miss Kashimura?
[SANA]
Miss Kashimura?
I like the sound of that!
Miss Kashimura! [laughs]
[SANA] I wanna talk about
the girl that was with you.
The one who did all that
mean stuff the other day.
What do you want to
know about Hatori?
[SANA] Obviously,
you care about her a lot.
But why? She's evil.
She's not.
And I care about her because,
well, she's my friend.
[SANA]
Your best friend?
[AYUMU]
Yes.
[SANA]
So, you guys are close?
Yeah.
We've known each other a long
time, ever since the 1st grade.
[SANA]
First grade?
Huh?
[SANA]
Oh, you mean school.
You go to school?
[AYUMU]
Sure.
Wait, are you saying you don't?
[SANA]
Nope. I don't.
I've heard that
it's fun, though.
It is.
I'm not a big fan of
studying or anything,
but I get to see my friends,
so that's cool.
[SANA sighs]
[AYUMU]
You know,
Hatori always loved
going to school,
but she doesn't come anymore.
[SANA]
Mm...
It sucks.
I want to find a way
to fix everything
so I can see her again.
But how?
She's got this awful power,
and I can't help.
[AYUMU] I feel lost.
I don't know what to do.
[SANA] It sounds like you
feel frazzled, too.
[AYUMU] Hm? That's the
word you used before.
I don't know what it means.
[SANA]
Frazzled means frazzled.
[AYUMU]
Hm. Want some?
[SANA gasping]
Ahh... So yummy.
I think it may even be
as good as pancakes.
[laughing]
The second I finish
lecturing her,
she closes her eyes and
starts talking in her sleep.
[SANAE]
Have you seen this?
[ZOROKU]
Hm?
The bathroom is so
much bigger now.
And it's cute, too!
Hey! Maybe I'll move in
and make this my room.
[SANA]
You seem like a good person.
Why would you be friends
with someone evil like Hatori?
[HATORI'S MOM] Aw, you're a
clingy one today, aren't you?
Are you feeling all right?
[HATORI]
Hey, Mom.
I'm gonna stay
with you forever, okay?
[HATORI'S MOM laughs]
Where is this coming from?
Of course you will.
[HATORI]
Mom.
[crash]
[HATORI]
Mm?
What is this doing here?
What is this place?
[rustling]
[HATORI]
Uh!
[SANAE]
Whoa. Those look great!
Go up and tell Sana
it's time to eat.
Sure!
Food is ready!
Hey, Sana!
[laughing]
Oh, wow! Look at that.
There's a tiny door here.
Oh!
She's gotten pretty
smart when it comes
to using her power, huh?
--[door creaking]
--Too smart.
[BOTH]
Hm?
Aw, how cu--
[ZOROKU grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[ZOROKU, SANAE]
"Went to catch the evil girl"?
[HATORI]
That's weird.
This area is different, like it
was drawn by a little kid.
[SANA]
Ha, ha, ha! Oh, good, you came!
Uh, I mean-- Ha!
I caught you!
You're mine now!
[HATORI]
Um, who are you?
[SANA laughs]
That's right!
You can't tell
who I am, can you?
Well, I'm a grown up,
and I'm very scary!
I made this place.
And you know what that means?
It means you're basically
inside my tummy!
I bet that makes you
feel scared, huh?
Good, you evil girl!
[HATORI] I don't need
you to tell me I'm evil.
I already know that I am.
[SANA]
Uh?
Maybe I can't see your face,
but it doesn't matter.
You don't scare me!
[SANA]
Uh...
[SANA stutters]
You're lying. I know you are!
How could you not
be scared of me?
I can do anything!
I could crush you like
a bug if I wanted to.
Or lock you up in a dungeon.
Like, a really scary dungeon.
With no food or bathroom breaks.
I get it now.
You're the girl I met
back in Harajuku.
[SANA]
No! Am not!
You're lying.
[SANA]
I already told you!
I'm a grownup, and I'm really
scary, and you've never met me.
Ever.
Grownups don't go around
saying they're grownups.
[SANA grunts]
Drop the act.
I know more about
lying than I used to,
and that's exactly
what you're doing.
You're just a
stupid little girl.
[SANA]
Did you say something?
[HATORI]
Forget it. I'm leaving.
[SANA]
Wait! Ow!
It's too cramped in here!
I won't let you get away.
You're trying to run
because you're evil.
You do bad things.
Yes, I know.
It's not like it was
an accident that I turned evil.
Uh... But--But you're
not supposed to do
mean things to people.
You'll get yelled at.
Yeah, maybe. But I don't care.
[SANA gasping]
[HATORI]
Don't you get it?
I'm a witch.
A witch with evil powers.
I'm not a normal human anymore.
I'm alone now.
There's no one on my side.
[SANA]
That's not true.
There is one person.
One single person left in the
world who cares about me.
But that doesn't matter anymore.
Not now. After I've
ruined everything.
Wait, you did?
[HATORI]
Like I said before...
...I know I'm evil.
[HATORI]
You could never understand.
No one can
understand how I feel.
[SANA] She really is
as evil as I thought.
[AYUMU] Even after
everything she's done,
she's still a good
person inside.
[SANA]
No. That's impossible.
If she was good, she wouldn't
have hurt people.
She wouldn't have turned Zoroku
and everyone else all weird.
[AYUMU]
The Hatori I know is very kind.
She's a little shy but super
smart--much smarter than me.
She's cute and friendly.
Cares about her family.
I always wanted to
be more like her.
Maybe then, I could've
become a witch, too.
[SANA grunts]
Let me by.
[SANA]
No.
I don't have anything
else to say to you.
[SANA]
Too bad!
I'm all frazzled now.
Ugh! I don't get it!
Don't get what?
It's simple, right?
You brought me here because
you wanted to make me pay.
So, get it over with
or let me leave.
[SANA]
Shut up and let me think!
After what you did,
I knew you were evil,
but she got me confused.
I asked about you,
and she said you were kind.
[gasps]
[SANA] Would she lie?
She's a good person.
She tried to find me
so that I could help you.
It doesn't make sense!
Hold on. Who is "she"?
[SANA] I hate being
frazzled all the time!
I'm so sick of it!
[HATORI]
Who were you talking about?
[SANA]
Uh...
That doorway...
It showed up in my house,
which means you
know where I live.
Who told you?!
No way...
Ayu told you where to find me?
[SANA]
I... I don't know.
[HATORI]
Quit lying to me!
No. Really, I, uh--
I don't know.
[HATORI]
This is an order!
Tell me truthfully if Ayu
was the one who sent you!
[SANA gasps]
[SANA]
Uh...
[HATORI]
Uh? What was that?
What's wrong with my power?
Uh...
[rumbling]
[SANA groans, screams]
[HATORI yelps]
[LAB MAN A] Abnormal situation
in Wonderland.
[LAB WOMAN A]
Energy emission increased.
[LAB MAN B]
Spatial wave factor rising.
[LAB MAN A] Abnormality
detected in Hidakamioka.
[LAB MAN B]
Quantum entanglement observed.
Jodorowsky space
is about to collapse.
What's happening in there?
[LAB MAN A]
Alert level upgrading to yellow!
[NORIKO]
All these abnormalities.
What's going on?
Something's very wrong
in Wonderland.
[GIRL A]
Hm? What's that thing?
[LAB MAN A] A giant Ferris
wheel appeared in Kyoto?
[LAB WOMAN A] Dreams of Alice
are popping up everywhere!
[LAB MAN C] Let's get
an exact count, if we can.
Ichijo, hey,
something is going on!
Wonderland is expanding!
We don't have
all the details yet,
but we've never seen
something like this!
[AYUMU] Kashimura said she
was going to Hatori's house.
If she's there to help,
Hatori won't mind, right?
[phone vibrates]
Yeah, hey, Mom. What's up?
Is something wrong?
I'm not far from home.
[AYUMU] Hatori, why?
What do you mean she's gone?
[SANAE] How does it look?!
Any sign of Sana yet?
[ZOROKU grunting]
[ZOROKU sighs]
You going somewhere?
[ZOROKU]
I want to take a look around.
[door opens, slams]
Huh? Mm.
Hey, Dad. Long day?
Yeah. Where's your mother?
Not here.
Hatori's gone missing,
so Mom went with her mother
to look for her.
[AYUMU'S DAD]
I see.
[AYUMU'S DAD] I got a call
about Hatori earlier, too.
I'll go out and help
them look for her.
[AYUMU'S DAD]
Where's Daiki?
He already had dinner
and went to bed.
[AYUMU'S DAD]
Hm.
I want you to do the same, Ayu.
Understand?
[AYUMU]
Can't I--
[AYUMU'S DAD]
No.
I know you're worried
about your friend,
but you're much too young
to be out at this time of night.
[AYUMU exhales]
It'll be all right.
Hatori's got a good head
on her shoulders.
She'll turn up soon.
[door opens]
[door slams]
Who's this evil girl
Sana's gone after?
The research facility was shut
down, so no one from there.
[door opens]
[SANAE]
How'd it go?
Any sign of her?
[ZOROKU]
No.
There's never any telling
where she'll wander off to.
You know Sana.
Do you think she's okay?
[ZOROKU]
Well, if nothing else,
she'll come home
when she gets hungry.
--[phone vibrates]
--[gasps]
[ZOROKU]
Yes, hello?
You've got
perfect timing, Ichijo.
Yeah, something's come up.
Yes, right. She's been
gone for a while now.
[ICHIJO]
I suspected as much.
[ZOROKU]
What's going on?
I don't have all
the details yet,
but a few hours ago, something
strange happened in Wonderland.
We're having a hard time
accessing it right now,
so all we have at the
moment is speculation.
But I'm fairly certain that
Sana is trapped inside.
[BOTH gasp]
What's more--
it appears that she's
not alone inside there.
Someone else is with her.
I'm about to enter into
Wonderland myself. I'd--
[ZOROKU] In that case,
I'm coming with you.
[ICHIJO]
You don't understand!
Wonderland is expanding.
It's very dangerous right now.
[ZOROKU]
All the more reason I should go.
My granddaughter's trapped
someplace, and is in danger.
It's my job to go after her and
bring her back home safely.
[gasping]
[bang]
[SANA]
Hey! I need help!
[banging]
[SANA]
Is anybody out there? Help!
[gasps]
Not such a big,
scary grownup now.
[SANA]
You shut up!
I'm stuck in here.
It won't open.
[HATORI]
Asking for my help?
I shouldn't need it.
Just thinking about getting out
of here would normally
be enough for me. I'm serious!
It works. Well, usually.
[HATORI]
Mm?
[SANA grunting]
[screaming]
[HATORI]
This girl sure is stubborn.
Why doesn't she
just ask me for help?
And I wonder what
she'd do if I gave it.
[SANA groaning]
[HATORI screams]
[HATORI]
That was easier than I expected.
I've never been that strong--
not nearly as strong as Ayu.
Is she just really weak?
[HATORI]
Hey. Do you know where we are?
I know you don't like me,
but I really need
to get back home.
You've shown me how powerful you
are and proven you can beat me.
I'll apologize,
if you want me to.
Just please, let me go home.
[SANA]
Yeah, see, well...
[SANA] The thing is,
I'm not sure, but...
...it's possible...
...we might be...
stuck here awhile.
[gasps]
[SANA]
"The Queen and the Witch."