[stomach growls]
[SANA groans quietly]
Brr. Freezing!
[SANA groans]
--[thud]
--[SANA yelps]
Huh? What was that?
[SANA whines]
Ow, ow...
What's going on?
I was trying to reach
the cord on the light.
I made a jump for it,
and I hit my head.
Ah-choo!
I think you'll live.
Now, go get the paper.
What? It's so cold!
[ZOROKU]
It's your chore, isn't it?
Aw... No fair, making
me go out in the cold.
[SANA squeals]
I'll freeze if I go out there.
[ZOROKU]
Not if you do it quickly.
[SANA]
Hmph.
Hah, gotcha!
[ZOROKU]
Sana!
Don't forget to wash your face
before breakfast, all right?
[SANA]
Aww...
[SANAE yawns]
G'morning, Grandpa...
[ZOROKU]
Yep.
[SANAE]
It's so cold!
[SANAE sighs]
[ZOROKU]
Hey, no going back to sleep now.
Practice today?
[SANAE]
No. Night-night.
[ZOROKU]
Get up.
There's coffee right there.
[SANAE groans]
Must have sugar.
Beautiful sugar.
[ZOROKU]
You have feet. Get it yourself.
[SANA whimpers]
[chuckles]
[SANA]
Too hot! Ow, ow, ow!
What happened?
Um, I was washing
my face and the water spilled.
[ZOROKU]
I know you're lying.
You were using your power again.
Stop goofing off and wash up.
If you think about it...
...my power is technically
part of my body, too.
It's like using my ha--
Don't split hairs
with me, young lady.
[SANA yelps]
He's being unreasonable.
Grandpa's just a little
worried about you, that's all.
I don't see why.
You do have more
stamina than you used to,
but you still get tired easily.
And feverish, also. He wants
you to strengthen your body
instead of relying
on your power.
[SANA groans]
I still don't think it's fair.
[SANAE chuckles] Okay, so how
do you want your hair?
[
I'll let you pick.
Right, just leave it to me!
[SANAE]
Gotta go. See ya!
Come home as soon as you can!
[SANAE]
I will!
[SANA]
Sanae headed off for school.
[ZOROKU]
Okay.
[SANA] Hey, shouldn't we be
leaving for the shop soon?
[ZOROKU] Yeah,
just gimme a couple minutes.
How long's it gonna
take you to smoke that thing?
I'm so bored!
[ZOROKU] If you're bored, then
do the homework Ichijo gave you.
But I did it already!
All that "math" stuff
is really easy.
Yeah? That's impressive.
I know, right?
What's wrong?
[SANA]
Hey!
Wonder whose cat that is.
Oh! You know what
that pattern reminds me of?
[ZOROKU]
Hmm?
Come on, Zoroku! The pig!
Right, the pig.
[SANA] ♪ Piggy, piggy,
spotted kitty, oink! ♪
You're in a good mood.
How come?
No reason, I just like to sing!
♪ The bell went jingle, jingle,
and the kitty ran away. ♪
♪ Tell me, pretty spotted kitty,
where do you live? ♪
Would you like to be
a singer when you grow up?
A singer?
Hey, that could be fun!
And now for a song
about a grasshopper!
♪ Hop a long
a little grasshopper, ♪
♪ playing in the sun! ♪
[SANA groans]
[ZOROKU] We haven't even
been walking for ten minutes.
Yeah, I know.
I'm not tired!
[ZOROKU]
Well, let's keep going, then.
[gasps]
Sana!
Ah! That guy
doesn't have to walk!
No fair! What is that thing?
Before using your power,
try solving the
problem yourself.
And tell me if you get tired.
[SANA]
Ah...
Oh, hey! Good morning, Boss-man!
We've already
started loading the flowers.
Good work.
We'll leave after this one's
had the chance to rest a bit.
Good morning...
Hey, you look pale.
You okay?
[ZOROKU]
Hold it up a little higher.
Are you in charge of
bouquets today, Chinatsu?
Yep, sure am.
Whatcha think?
Why's it white?
It was made
to match a specific dress.
Cool!
Sana. Stand
over there and hold it.
[SANA]
Mm
All right. You pass.
It looks good.
Woo! That's what I like to hear!
I owe you big time
for this, Sana.
You're the best model
a girl could ask for!
I wouldn't mind helping more!
If you're sure you don't mind.
Well?
[SANA groans]
Let me, that one's heavy.
[SANA]
Uh...
Come on. We're going.
[SANA] Oh, okay.
Trash goes in the trash can!
[SANA]
Ow! I stepped on my hair.
[ZOROKU]
You should be more careful.
Feeling less tired now?
Yeah, thanks!
[sniffs]
Smells good.
We've got some
fragrant ones today.
[SANA]
Yeah!
Let's get going.
Movin' out.
[ZOROKU]
We're from Kashimura Floral.
[STAFF A] Come with me.
I'll show you where to set up.
So, what's today's event?
[CHINATSU]
It's an engagement party.
What's an "engagement"?
[CHINATSU] Basically, it's
when people make a promise
to marry each other.
And then they have
a party to celebrate it?
Who do you think
you're going to marry
once you're all grown up, Sana?
[SANA]
Hmm... I don't know.
[CHINATSU]
Not yet!
The heavy one.
[ICHIRO]
Yep.
Go and move
the car to the lot, would you?
Okay.
[ZOROKU groans]
[SANA]
You all right?
Yeah. It's touching
the ground again.
[SANA]
Huh? What is?
[ZOROKU]
Careful not to trip on it.
[SANA]
Uh...
Maybe you should
think about getting a haircut.
Uh...
[CHINATSU]
Sana! It's frozen over.
Come and look, there's ice.
[SANA]
Ooh, really?
Take that and put it
somewhere out of the way.
[SANA]
Okay!
[ZOROKU]
Finished.
It's so beautiful
I could almost cry!
There are so many flowers!
[ZOROKU]
Hmm?
Hey, what're these called?
[ZOROKU]
They're lilies.
--These are, too?
--[ZOROKU] Yeah.
--And these, right?
--[ZOROKU] That's right.
[SANA giggles]
I'll go outside with her
to help clean up, cool?
Good. Thank you.
[CHINATSU]
Hey, Sana! Wait for me.
How's it going, Kashimura?
Coming along?
We just finished
setting the room up.
Do you see any changes
you'd like to make?
[CHIKA]
Wow, it's fantastic!
Everything's so pretty!
[SAWAKI chuckles]
[gasps]
[ZOROKU] Your fiancée
seems to be awfully young.
Yeah, well, it's a long story.
What about you, Kashimura?
I didn't know you had such a
young granddaughter.
Yeah, well, that's
a long story, too.
[CHIKA]
Oh, how pretty!
Hey, what are you doing?
Me? Well, I'm having
my engagement party here.
An engagement?
That's a promise to get married!
I learned that today.
[CHIKA giggles]
But what's
"getting married" mean?
Huh? That's sort of
a tough question.
Let's see here.
What is marriage?
It's when you and
someone you love become family.
[SANA]
Oh...
Ah! What am I saying?
That's so embarrassing!
Are you okay?
Come on, Sana. It's time to go.
--[SANA] Mm!
--Is he your grandpa?
Uh-huh! You can tell 'cause
he's really, really old!
Well, bye!
[SANA] One, two, three,
four, five, one hundred!
Why not wait until
I'm finished washing?
We can chat.
[SANA groans]
So, how was work today?
--We set up for a fancy party.
--Fun!
And I learned what
getting engaged means.
It's when people make
a promise to get married.
You're learning so much, Sana!
[SANA]
Hmph! That's not all!
Getting married means
you and someone you love
become, uh, family!
[SANAE giggles]
Wow!
What's a "family," though?
[SANAE]
Uh...
[giggles]
[SANA yelps]
That's an easy one to answer.
You're my family, Sana!
[SANA]
Hey, get off!
Got it.
This family thing's confusing.
Sanae says she's my family.
That's good to know.
What about Zoroku?
Is he my family, too?
And what exactly is family?
Now I'm all frazzled!
[ZOROKU]
Hmm...
[SANAE]
What?!
You're not really going to
cut your hair, are you?
[SANA]
Yeah.
It's so long she trips
over it five times a day.
Aw, man, I look forward
to doing it every morning.
It's one of the
best parts of my day.
Don't worry.
It won't be forever.
Hair grows fast,
just like weeds.
When it grows back,
you can do it again.
Oh! Yeah? Really?
You'll see,
it'll grow back in no time!
Hooray!
So, where will she get it cut?
You aren't going to
do it for her, are you?
[ZOROKU]
No.
[SANA]
Huh? He can't cut it?
A florist only cuts flowers.
If you need somebody
to cut your hair,
you have to go to a beautician.
[ZOROKU]
Don't be snarky.
[SANAE]
Mm!
Where do we find a beautician?
[SANA]
What is that?
What is that?!
What is this crazy place?!
It's a beauty salon.
It smells funny!
Don't go running around.
[STYLIST A]
Hello, thank you for waiting.
[ZOROKU] I have an
appointment under Kashimura.
Okay, let me take a look.
Yes, I see you right here.
[ZOROKU] How long will
the appointment take?
[STYLIST A]
Since she's just getting a cut
and not doing any color,
I don't think it should
take more than an hour.
Sana, I'm going
to leave for a bit.
Why? What are you doing?
[ZOROKU]
Hmm. Nothing much.
I have some errands
to run, that's all.
[SANA]
Huh?
[STYLIST A]
All right, are you ready?
[SANA]
Uh... Yeah.
Hmm.
[STYLIST A giggles]
Let's talk style.
Your grandpa suggested
going with a bob.
What do you think about that?
Uh, what's a "bob"?
[SHOP WORKER A]
Thanks, have a nice day!
[NAITO]
Here, as requested.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm...
I'll take one, too.
[WAITER A]
Coming right up.
I'm surprised.
You got these quick.
Yeah, and it wasn't
exactly easy, either.
Had to call in a favor or two.
[ZOROKU]
Yeah. Thanks a lot.
It should probably be me
thanking you, though.
Sana's a lot of work, but you're
taking good care of her.
[ZOROKU] Every day's
more hectic than the last.
Can't be easy to keep up
with the young 'uns at your age.
--Huh?
--I'm just kidding.
Anyway, how's the pig?
[NAITO]
Hmm?
You know, the spotted
one I had you take in.
I think it would make Sana
happy if she could see it.
--Maybe we could--
--Oh, sorry. I ate it.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm?!
Look at your face!
I'm just joking.
[STYLIST A]
Well, what do you think?
[gasps]
It's so light now! Amazing!
You like the way
the back looks, too?
Yeah!
Just sit tight till your
grandpa gets back, okay?
Sure!
[giggles] I can't wait to
see what Zoroku thinks!
[ZOROKU]
Where is she?!
♪ Zoroku, Zoroku,
where did you go? ♪
♪ I'll find you!
I'll find you! ♪
♪ I'll look high and low! ♪
Hey, Sana. You get a haircut?
Yep! It's lighter now
So, where's Roku?
He's running late,
so I decided to look for him.
[SHOP WORKER B]
Well, good luck!
See ya!
♪ My head feels so light! ♪
♪ Hooray! Hooray! ♪
♪ Like a bubble that's
going to float away! ♪
♪ A bubble floating. ♪
♪ Floating up to the sky. ♪
♪ So high! Until it
pops and falls. ♪
♪ Falls like rain! ♪
♪ Pretty raindrops falling! ♪
♪ But when it gets cold,
they turn to snow. ♪
That smells good!
[groans] I don't have
any money to buy one.
[KITTY meows]
[SANA]
Hey, there.
Do you want a crépe
as much as I do?
[KITTY meows]
[SANA]
Come back!
[ZOROKU pants]
Hey! I wonder
where that cat ran off to.
Chilly! Guess I'll go home.
[SANA]
Wait. I don't know where I am.
Before using your power,
try solving the
problem yourself.
[gasps]
[SANA]
Which way is it...?
Are we eating soon,
Mommy? I'm hungry!
Don't worry, sweetie.
We'll be home before
you know it, okay?
[SANA]
Zoroku...
[ZOROKU]
I see. Thank you.
[cell phone vibrates]
Yes, hello?
You found her?
[sobbing]
[POLICEMAN A]
Yes. A passerby called us
when they noticed
her wandering around.
That's right.
I thought I told you
to wait for me at the salon.
[SANA groans]
I know. I'm sorry.
I was running late,
and for that I'm sorry.
[SANA sighs]
[ZOROKU]
If it happens again,
just call me like
you did before.
[SANA]
Hmm...?
[ZOROKU] Though if we
could avoid ending up
in a shipping container,
that'd be nice.
You mean that
I can use my power?
[ZOROKU] I don't want
you to rely on your power
for everything. That doesn't
mean you can never use it.
It's part of what makes
you who you are.
[SANA gasps]
[ZOROKU] You just need
to learn to use it wisely.
[SANA]
Zoroku, you smell.
Were you smoking?
[ZOROKU]
Ho?
[SANA]
I said you stink!
[ZOROKU]
Hey Keep it down.
Thanks for the haircut.
I really like it!
Yeah? Good.
It's so light!
Nice.
You should cut yours, too!
[ZOROKU]
Hmm?
[SANA] It'll be fun!
They shampoo it
for you and everything!
[ZOROKU]
Oh, you liked that part?
[SANA]
Yeah! It felt good!
Aw! You look so adorable!
The lady said it's called a bob.
It's perfect on you!
This is for you.
[gasps]
What is it?
[SANA giggles]
[laughs]
A pig! A pig!
Flying pig! Oink. Oink!
Enough messing with the light.
[SANA]
Uh. Oh, hey. What's up?
Is the bath ready?
No. Could you please
come downstairs?
[SANA]
Uh...
Come on in and sit down with us.
[SANA] Uh... Are we having
dessert or something?
Is everything
about food with you?
Behave yourself, Grandpa.
That's not a
very nice thing to say.
I guess that's
a "no" on dessert, then.
That's too bad.
Just come over here
and sit down.
There's something
we need to talk about.
[SANA]
Uh...
[SANAE giggles]
[ZOROKU]
These are adoption papers.
What do "adoption papers" do?
If we sign them.
it means that you will
become an official member
of our household.
[SANAE]
Hmm.
[SANA]
Uh.
[ZOROKU] That way, if something
were to happen to Sanae and me,
you would be taken care of.
And when you're ready,
you could even go to school.
You would be
Sana Kashimura,
of the Kashimura household.
I'd be Sana Kashimura?
We'd be a family for real.
[gasps]
A family?
Sana Kashimura.
Sana Kashimura!
[giggles]
Hi, I'm Sana Kashimura!
Yeah, you are!
No need to make
such a ruckus about it.
[SANA]
Does this mean we're married?
[SANAE]
Ah? No, silly!
[SANA hums]
I did it!
[SANA giggles]
[SANA squeals]
[SANA]
"Friends."