[HATORI] Our story begins
long ago in a faraway land,
where there lived an
unfortunate girl.
Little did she know
that the real trouble
was only beginning.
[CLERK A]
I'm very sorry, ma'am,
but I'm afraid at
this point in March,
these are all we have available.
[HATORI'S MOM]
Thank you. I understand.
I'm sorry, Hatori.
You'll have to choose one
of these, alright?
[HATORI]
Mm-hmm.
Here, Mom. I want this one.
[HATORI'S MOM]
Oh?
Right here.
This is where the school
insignia would normally go.
[HATORI]
I'm sorry, Mom.
[HATORI'S DAD]
You're bringing that up again?
It happened over two years ago.
[HATORI'S DAD]
Hatori is a smart girl.
She'll get another shot with the
middle school entrance exams.
[HATORI'S MOM]
This is what you always do.
Try to postpone the issue
like that'll make it go away.
[HATORI'S MOM]
Sending her to public school
for three more years.
[HATORI'S DAD] It was your
idea to not have her test
for a backup school.
[HATORI'S MOM] I thought
narrowing the options
would force her to work
that much harder.
[sighs]
Sure turned out well.
Don't give me that!
What about you?
What have you done
to help these past years?
You've never taken
her entrance exams seriously!
You wouldn't listen
to any of my concerns.
I'm the one who
got her extra lessons.
researched all the schools!
[HATORI]
Are you listening, God?
The thing is, Mom and Dad
don't like each other anymore,
and it's my fault for being
such a useless daughter.
I don't need any
presents for my birthday,
or Christmas either.
I promise I'll study hard.
I'll do anything.
But please, please, God.
Make Mom and Dad
be nice to each other
and start getting along again!
[DAIKI, AYUMU]
Time to eat!
[AYUMU'S DAD]
Ayumu.
Stop gulping
your food like that.
You know Daiki will copy you.
Sure, Dad.
Well, dear.
We'll be at your
match today, as usual.
[AYUMU]
Okay, Mom, sounds good.
See you then!
Good luck out there!
[DAIKI]
I'll cheer for you!
[cell phone vibrates]
Oh, the match!
Good morning!
I, uh...
[HATORI]
Are we having breakfast?
Anyway, Ayumu's
playing a match later today.
Want to go cheer for her,
like we used to do?
The three of us together?
[gasps]
[HATORI'S MOM]
That's a great idea!
What?
Who's Ayumu?
She's one of
Hatori's good friends,
a real lively young girl.
Oh, yeah.
She's the one with
the short hair, right?
Let's go to the match.
It's been too long!
[HATORI'S MOM] I'll go get some
lunches packed for us, then.
[HATORI'S DAD] We can just
pick up food somewhere.
[gasps]
[HATORI] One day, a good
witch appeared before
the unfortunate little girl
and looked down at her
with kind eyes.
"What is your wish?"
the good witch asked.
And the little girl
said to her,
"I wish everybody would be nice
to each other all the time!"
[HATORI] Then the witch
smiled and said, "Very well.
Listen, and I will teach
you some magic words."
[HATORI]
But the girl was confused.
She didn't know how to use
the words the witch gave her.
You shouldn't walk
till the signal tells you to.
[BOTH gasp]
[BOY A]
Hey! Hurry up, already!
[BOY B] I hope the
basketball court is open!
[BOY C] The guys from the other
class might've beaten us there.
[HATORI] You aren't
supposed to run in the halls.
[gasps]
Do you see that, too?
[BOYS]
Huh?
[BOY D]
Come on, guys!
--[BOY B] Yeah, let's go!
--[HATORI] That was weird.
I wonder what just happened.
[AYUMU] I've never
seen anything like it.
Hmm.
[AYUMU] Do you think maybe...
it was magic?
It must be.
Yeah, remember that guy
crossing the street before?
[gasps]
He stopped.
I bet you made him
do it using your magic.
Ah.
You've obviously
got some kind of superpower!
No, that's crazy.
Well. why
don't you try it again?
What?
Test out your magic.
[HATORI]
Um... I dunno.
Whatever this is,
I think it's real.
You've used it twice already
without even meaning to!
I guess it can't hurt to try.
[gasps]
Stop moving.
Wow, it worked!
Did you see?
[gasps]
Ayumu?
Hey! Wake up!
Hmm? Something wrong?
You look worried.
[AYUMU]
Whoa! Look!
The experiment worked!
You really can do magic!
[HATORI] You think
that's what this is?
[AYUMU] Yeah, I do!
What else could it be?
It's like...
...I've turned into
a witch or something.
[AYUMU]
Yeah, but you're a good witch!
Huh...?
[AYUMU]
Try it again.
[gasps]
Come on! Do more!
Go for a walk.
I want to see them dance.
[AYUMU]
Oh, wow.
They do what I say, too!
Okay, one more. Don't move!
[HATORI]
Ayumu.
[AYUMU]
Hmm?
Are you afraid of me now?
Please, there's no way
I could ever be afraid of you.
'Kay? I'll always
be by your side.
[HATORI] "Listen, and I will
teach you some magic words.
Use them, and you can grant
yourself any wish.
Everybody around you will do
whatever you tell them to."
[HATORI] "However, you must
only use the words for good.
Do that, and you will
become a good witch.
But if you use
the words for evil,
then you will surely
become an evil witch."
But the little girl
was far too excited about
her new power to listen
to the good witch.
You know, your mom
is really pretty, Hatori.
And she always seems so happy.
Maybe sometime,
she could give my mom
a little fashion advice.
[HATORI giggles]
So, has she
always been this cool?
At the beginning of the term,
she seemed, I dunno, kinda...
...intimidating?
[GIRL C] It's like
she's a different person now.
[HATORI gasps]
[HATORI grunts]
[stomach growls]
[HATORI gasps]
Mom? Dad?
Hey!
[HATORI]
Just look at them.
[HATORI] "If you use
the words for evil,
then you will surely
become an evil witch."
[HATORI]
Some part of me knew.
[AYUMU sighs]
[HATORI] It didn't make
sense that Mom and Dad
were suddenly getting along.
That they were happy again.
I knew it was just
because of the magic.
[HATORI] But I guess I didn't
want to accept the truth.
[HATORI] I didn't know
God was so cruel.
What good is having this power
if it can't fix anything?
[HATORI]
So, what do I do now?
As long as I'm here,
I'll be forcing
my parents to live a lie.
[AYUMU]
I don't know.
I have to leave them.
[AYUMU]
Okay, then.
I'm coming with you.
What? But why?
Because... I used your magic.
I did bad things with it,
just like you.
So, we're the same.
[SANA hums]
[SANA]
Hey, what time is it?
I hate to tell ya,
but it's 10:46.
So, about two minutes since
the last time you asked.
Oh. is that all?
Sorry.
I guess you're really
excited about seeing
your friends again, huh?
[SANA]
Mm-hmm!
These friends of
yours are twins, correct?
That's right! Asahi and Yonaga.
[ZOROKU]
Sana.
Will you throw out
those things in the back?
What are they called?
Uh, you know
they're green and soft.
Nope, you've lost me.
Wait! I know!
The squishy things.
Yeah, right, those.
Sure, no problem.
Leave it to me!
[SANA hums]
[SANA]
Here you are! Now, listen up!
First I'm gonna wring you out,
then I'm gonna throw you away!
[SANA]
Squish...!
Gross, but so cool!
[hums]
Squish!
[SANA] Boy, are they
gonna be surprised!
It hasn't even been that long.
But I've learned
so many new things.
Clearly, I'm amazing!
[YONAGA]
Hey, wait, slow down!
You shouldn't walk
so far ahead of me.
We don't want to get lost or--
[ASAHI]
Don't worry about it!
It'll be easy to find
our way around
with the map Sana sent me!
[YONAGA]
Um... are you sure
you're reading it
correctly, Sis?
[YONAGA]
Like I was saying...
Yeah, okay.
Cut me some slack.
Everybody makes mistakes.
Let's see here.
[ASAHI]
Hey, look where we are!
[YONAGA]
Takeshita Street?
We've never been here before.
Hey, Sis, are you coming?
[ASAHI]
Yonaga.
[YONAGA]
Yeah?
[ASAHI] How long would it
take us to get to Urahara?
[YONAGA]
Oh, no! Sana's waiting for us!
You don't want to
let her down, do you?
[ASAHI] Of course not,
but there's still so much
we haven't gotten to see!
I thought, just for a bit.
Maybe?
Well, we could always ask Sana
if she would come
explore the city with us.
[ASAHI gasps]
That's a perfect idea!
Let's ask her!
That way, we can go sightseeing
and hang out with her
at the same time!
[YONAGA]
Uh-huh.
Right! Let's go find
Sana and see if she'll
come play with us!
[YONAGA]
Yeah!
[HATORI]
This is an order.
Stop.
[SANA] The green things
are taken care of.
So what's up next?
[SANA]
Uh, what are you doing?
Hey. What's going on, Zoroku?
[SANA]
Talk to me.
Is this a weird joke
or something?
Zoroku?
Zoroku!
Your arm will tire
if you leave it up like that.
You should put it down.
And don't stand around
yelling and blocking the street
like a couple of children.
It isn't polite.
[HATORI]
This is an order.
Move out of my way.
So, what do you want?
Oh, uh. I don't know.
The one with
strawberries, maybe.
Looks yummy.
[HATORI] And one kiwi
with whipped cream.
[AYUMU] So, what
are we going to do now?
[HATORI]
I'm not sure.
I guess we just do whatever we
want until we're out of money,
and then we can get
a job if we need to.
[HATORI] I figure, you've got
magic, you can get a job,
--no matter how old you are.
--[AYUMU] Yeah...
[HATORI] We'll go somewhere
nobody knows us and find work.
When we've been there a
while and saved up enough,
we'll move on to the next place.
It'll be an adventure.
[AYUMU]
Hmm...
Why don't we check out
the city from up there?
[AYUMU]
Sure.
[AYUMU] It's smaller than it
seems on the ground.
[HATORI]
Yeah, it is.
This is a nice view, huh?
I guess there are some
benefits to having magic.
[AYUMU]
It's so quiet.
Like everyone else
has disappeared,
and you and I are
the only ones left.
[HATORI]
Yep.
Are you sure?
[AYUMU]
Hmm?
[HATORI]
About coming with me.
You don't have to do it.
[AYUMU]
Why? Don't you want me with you?
[HATORI]
Yeah, of course.
I didn't mean it like that.
It's just that this whole
mess is my fault, not yours.
It was my stupid magic that
screwed everything up.
With me there, home
would never be normal.
I didn't have any choice.
Leaving my parents
was my only option.
You've still got a home you
can go back to, though.
I promised you,
remember?
That I'd stay by your side.
Witch or not,
you're still Hatori to me.
Thank you so much!
[HATORI]
Ayumu. I love you!
You're such a hot guy!
I know. Yeah, that's me.
The hot guy.
[CROWD moaning, groaning]
What's with them?
The magic shouldn't
have worn off yet.
[SANA]
What's wrong with you?
Is this some kind of prank?
Snap out of it!
--Say something, already!
--[AYUMU] Over there!
--[CROWD] Something, already...
--No! Not that!
That's not what I meant!
Agh! This is so wrong.
First Zoroku, now them.
It's like everyone except
me has turned into
an empty shell somehow.
I don't know.
What's going on here?
--[footsteps]
--[SANA] Hmm?
You're awake? How?
[sighs]
Hey, are you okay?
I'm... so tired.
I've never had to run
that far before.
Why doesn't the magic
affect you like everyone else?
Wait, magic?
What are you talking about?
Tell me... what's going on...
Who are you?
All these people...
are they okay?
Zoroku and the rest.
Everybody's acting so weird.
Just, tell me what's happening.
I'm all frazzled again,
and I hate that feeling!
[HATORI]
I don't understand.
[SANA]
Please, I have to know!
So, my magic
doesn't work on this girl.
Seems that way.
But why not?
This has never happened before.
[AYUMU]
Hey, are you a witch, too?
[SANA]
What?
Maybe you have the
answers we're looking for.
Tell me, why doesn't
Hatori's power affect you.
Huh?
Did you do
something to stop it?
Or say something, maybe?
Please just tell us
anything you know!
We need help!
We have to find a way
to get rid of the magic.
Ayumu. What are you saying?
Please, what do you know?
Wait. I'm confused.
What magic? Who are you?
Well, my name is Ayumu Miho.
And this is my friend, Hatori.
--Hey, stop it!
--No.
If it's true, if you
can control the magic,
maybe you can help Hatori get
rid of hers so she can go home!
[gasps]
I don't understand.
This is crazy.
All these people have been
turned into mindless robots.
[SANA] And... And...
You're telling me that...
...you did it?
The two of you did this to them?
It's your fault? It was you!
You did this to Zoroku!
She has one?
--What? How did it...?
--What's wrong?
[shrieks]
[shrieking continues]
--[HATORI grunts]
--[PEDESTRIAN B] Hey, look out.
[PEDESTRIAN C]
Sorry.
[PEDESTRIAN D]
Watch where you're going, man.
[PEDESTRIAN C]
It wasn't my fault.
This can't be.
Everyone's... awake again.
This is gonna be really fun!
[YONAGA]
Yeah, totally!
I'm so glad we get to see Sana.
[SANA]
You two.
[gasps]
[pants] You... You won't get
away with this, you hear me?
I won't let you!
[BOTH gasp]
[CROWD gasping]
[PEDESTRIAN E]
Hey, look at that!
[PEDESTRIAN F]
Whoa, what is it?
[PEDESTRIAN G]
A promotion?
[PEDESTRIAN C]
Why Santa, though?
[gasps]
[PEDESTRIAN H]
Okay, what just happened?
[PEDESTRIAN I]
You saw Santa Claus, too, right?
[SANA growls]
[HATORI gasps]
[gasps]
Hey, that's
never happened before.
[HATORI gasps]
This is an order.
Stop interfering.
[PEDESTRIAN J]
What are those, fireworks?
[PEDESTRIAN D]
Huh? Where?
Who are you?
Or what?
--That hurts!
--Let's all calm down.
Hey! You're hurting me! Stop it!
Please stop!
This isn't helping anything.
Shut up! She deserves this!
--What kind of person are you?
--That is enough!
[SANA]
Why? At least tell me.
Why...?
[SANA grunts]
Wait for me!
Hey! Come back!
You two-- Oh.
Out of energy.
[PEDESTRIAN K]
What happened to her?
[PEDESTRIAN E]
Is she all right?
[AYUMU]
Hatori?
Hey!
[HATORI]
When I use my magic on people,
they forget about it afterwards,
so it's like it never happened.
I told myself that made it okay.
[HATORI]
But she won't forget.
She watched everyone around her,
not just people on the street,
but her friends and family,
turn into soulless zombies.
And she was in the middle
of them, all alone.
[HATORI] She must have felt so
scared, so lost and confused.
I can't imagine how
terrifying it was for her.
What's wrong?
[HATORI]
Don't you see...?
It happened...
I really did turn
into an evil witch...
[SANA]
"Where the Cheshire Cat Smiles."