[SANA hums]
♪ You look thirsty,
yes you do! ♪
♪ But I've got water for you.
Are you feeling better now? ♪
♪ "We are. thank you!" ♪
Having a good morning so far?
Can't complain.
Hey! How's it going, Ichijo?
It's Ms. Ichijo, remember?
Put the watering can away.
You got it. I'm excited about
our train ride, Ichijo!
Ms. Ichijo!
Right!
She's hopeless.
[ICHIJO chuckles]
[gasps]
There are so many people!
[ICHIJO]
It's crowded on the weekend.
You think we should
take the subway?
Nah. She'll miss out
on the scenery if we do.
Sana, let's get our tickets.
Ah. What's a "ticket," anyway?
[ZOROKU] It's what
you use to get on a train.
See here, where it says "child"?
First, you want to push that.
[SANA]
Mm... This one?
[ZOROKU] Then, push the
button that matches the fare
to your destination.
What's half of 550?
Two hundred seventy-five!
[ZOROKU]
Then, select 270.
Uh. That's not half.
[ZOROKU] Yeah, well,
that's just how it works.
Don't ask me.
[SANA]
Okay...
[ZOROKU]
See, you put your ticket in.
Then, take it when it pops out.
Now you try it.
Uh, okay.
I got it back!
[turnstile beeps]
Hey, what's that?!
A card that works
the way a ticket does.
Aw, no fair!
I want one that beeps, too!
You won't be riding
enough to need one.
I want a beepy one!
[ICHIJO laughs]
[SANA gasps]
Looks like
somebody's having fun.
It's the first time
she's taken a trip like this.
[ZOROKU] Sorry, but this
is where I have to leave you.
No worries.
I'm more than
happy to look after her.
I want you to behave
and do as Ms. Ichijo says.
I will. Now go on.
You don't want
to be late, do you?
All right. I'll see you later.
Bye! Have fun at work!
[SANA hums]
[gasps]
Look at all that water!
[SANA laughs]
[ICHIJO chuckles]
That's what we call the ocean.
It's big.
Very.
[SANA]
Uh.
Ugh! Ew.
Something smells yucky.
[ICHIJO] Don't lean so far.
That's dangerous!
[SANA hums]
♪ La-La, la, la-la! ♪
There! Finished!
All right. Let me look it over.
[SANA hums quietly]
[ICHIJO]
You got everything correct!
You have a talent for numbers.
I know!
If you keep up this pace,
you'll complete
high school first-year math
before much longer.
We've already reached the
limit of what I can teach you,
so we'll have to talk to Naito.
Huh? That's all you know?
But math's so easy.
For some people.
I have a teaching license
for elementary school,
so I do know the basics.
But I just can't
keep up with you.
In math,
everything's straightforward,
with no fuzzy or gray areas.
Watering flowers
is complicated, though.
There are all these
different conditions
and variables, so it's harder.
You have to look at them every
day to see what they need.
What you really
seem to be struggling with
is word problems.
And reading, as well.
It would help if you could
focus for longer stretches.
Yeah, well, that kind
of stuff gets me all frazzled,
so I don't like it.
What do you mean, "frazzled"?
It's strange.
How do I explain it?
It's something I feel right
here, you know?
I don't like things
I can't understand.
I get all jumpy inside.
[ICHIJO]
Hmm... That makes sense.
You do have some trouble when
it comes to writing, as well.
Next week, I think we
should work a little harder
on language arts.
[SANA]
Huh? Wha-- Why?
Because that's it
for math today.
Now, it's time for
a social studies lesson.
Are we going somewhere?
Seeing as we're
already here in Yokohama,
we'll take advantage of it,
and pay a visit to
a nearby factory.
Naito made the arrangements.
Naito? He can do anything, huh?
[ICHIJO]
Ready to see a car factory?
[SANA]
Yeah!
[ZOROKU] I think it's a good
idea to exclusively use
flowers that are in season.
We can use blooms like
in these arrangements
if you want a natural look.
Wow! So pretty!
Yeah...
It'll be easiest
if you'll allow me
to choose the flowers we use.
I don't think we'll have
any problems keeping it
well within your budget.
That sounds perfect!
Don't you agree, Ko?
Sure, it's up to you.
[YOUNG WOMAN]
Come on! This is important.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm.
[SANA]
Zoroku!
[ZOROKU]
Hmm?
[SANA giggles]
Easy.
Are you done with work now?
That took a while!
Did you behave for Ms. Ichijo?
Of course. We went
to see a car factory!
It was super cool!
Everything's put
together by robots.
Is that so?
Anything happen
while I was gone?
No, nothing out of the ordinary.
Well, that's good.
Uh.
[ICHIJO gasps]
An error.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm...
[ASAHI]
Mm! This is good! Excuse me!
--I'll take 30 more pork buns!
--Thirty?
--What, do you not have that?
--Uh, sorry.
[ASAHI] Really?
What if I give a big tip?
No.
Okay, then. Just give me as many
as you do have! All of them!
Ah! There!
Wait for me, Sis,
I'm right behind you!
[ASAHI]
Hey, where have you been?
You're late. Don't go
wandering off on your own.
No fair!
You were the one who ran off
without saying anything!
How much stuff did you buy?
[ASAHI] I found these awesome
pork buns, so I bought them all.
Here, try one. You'll like it!
You shouldn't
have bought so much.
We need to be careful with
our money, remember?
What are you talking about?
The whole point of saving
it was so we could
eat until we exploded.
We haven't come anywhere
close to using it all yet.
[YONAGA]
Hey, wait. Hold on.
You were the one who said we
should go to as many places
as we could so we could
try different stuff.
We even picked some out,
but you've made so many
random stops, we haven't gone
anywhere we had planned.
[gasps]
'Cause plans
can always be changed.
--[YONAGA grunts]
--Now, stop wasting time.
The world is our oyster!
[YONAGA whines]
Thanks, have a good day.
Hey, Asahi.
We haven't done this in a while.
Gone shopping together, I mean.
Just you and me.
And, part of me
actually believed that we
never would again, you know?
And yet, here we are!
[gasps]
Come on! Let's make the most
of it. What do ya say?
Yeah. Sure!
[ASAHI]
Shops! Restaurants! Parks!
[YONAGA] Let's go!
Hey, look out behind you!
Careful!
[yelps]
Are you okay?
I'm sorry...
[SANA groans]
[YONAGA]
Sana...?
Ah
[TWINS gasp]
Stop right there!
--[ZOROKU] Hmm?
--[TWINS gasp]
[SANA]
They're running!
Okay, Operation 418.
Go after them.
Hey, come back here!
[yelps]
[MAN A]
What is that, a chain?
Ah! Stupid jerks!
[ASAHI]
Why did we run away?
[YONAGA]
I don't know.
But it's too late to
turn back now.
Agreed.
[TWINS]
In which case. Let's keep going!
You're not getting away.
Chain Net!
[gasps]
That wasn't very nice.
Robot!
There's no way I'm letting
you losers beat me at tag!
Motorbike!
--[MAN B] What is that?
--[WOMAN A] A motorcycle?
[SANA] Wait up!
Why are you running away?
Because we feel like it!
Why are you following us?
I don't know! Seeing you
just made me feel frazzled!
[ASAHI]
What did you say?!
[SANA] I said, I feel frazzled!
[GIRL A]
What's that, Mommy?
Some kind of circus, maybe?
Wow.
[MAN 7D]
Incredible.
[MAN 7C]
That's some serious stunt work.
They'll be the death of me.
Why won't you just stay still?
Obviously because we
don't want to see you!
Can't you take a hint for once?
What do you mean?
Why not?
Give me a reason,
or I'll never understand!
[gasps]
[TWINS]
Hey, what's wrong?
[SANA]
Error...
[FENRIR roars]
[SANA whimpers]
[TWINS gasp]
Operation 13-7.
Summon beast.
Fenrir.
All three of you will
be punished.
Number 51.
Operation 1-8.
--[TWINS grunt]
--[SANA gasps]
Deploy operation 516. Fenrir.
[FENRIR roars]
[GIRLS scream]
And now, 1-8.
[ICHIJO]
Accelerate!
[GIRLS scream]
[GIRLS groan]
[HOSTESS A] Good afternoon.
Do you have a reservation?
We do.
[gasps]
Sana Kashimura!
Right. Just a moment please.
Kashimura?
Ah. Yeah, that's my name now!
[TWINS]
Mm.
[ICHIJO]
As far as I can tell,
it appears to be a lump
of carbon again.
[ICHIJO]
That's right. It's fine.
We managed to convince
everyone who saw that
we were filming a movie.
But please take care of any
photos online for me.
Uh-huh.
The twins are still with us.
[TWINS groan]
Well, sit down already.
We're going to order.
[ASAHI]
Um, I don't know.
[YONAGA]
Maybe we should just go.
You apologized to Ms. Ichijo,
and that's what matters.
Go on, sit.
[TWINS]
Okay.
Now, food.
Do you two have
allergies to anything?
If not, I'll just order
whatever looks good.
Oh, no, that would be fine.
We don't.
And, uh, thank you!
[TWINS gasp]
[SANA growls]
It's just so confusing!
Tell me! Why?
Seeing you two
made me feel frazzled!
I don't like it!
It's all your fault
I feel this way!
[gasps]
I don't understand what
"frazzled" means, exactly.
Frazzled means frazzled, okay?
Sana.
[SANA groans]
[SANA] I feel like this all the
time lately.
I can't escape it.
And when you suddenly
showed up earlier,
it only made the feeling worse.
It didn't used to be like that.
[SANA]
What's going on?
It's like I'm myself
but not at the same time.
I never felt frazzled
like this when I was
at the research facility,
so why now?
I have to know!
[TWINS gasp]
Well, I just figured
you were mad at us
for running away.
Is that how you feel?
Angry?
[SANA]
Mm? I, uh...
Yeah. I am angry.
[gasps]
[ZOROKU]
Sit back down, Sana.
[SANA]
Right.
[TWINS groan]
[ZOROKU]
Don't be shy.
Sorry, your names were?
Oh! I'm Yonaga Hinagiri!
Well, introduce yourself, Sis.
Right! And I'm Asahi.
You should
eat before it gets cold.
[SANA growls]
[ASAHI]
Uh... Okay...
[YONAGA]
I guess...
This is tasty!
Super tasty!
[SANA]
So good, right?
[ASAHI]
Yeah, it's delicious!
[YONAGA]
Mm-hm!
[TWINS gasp]
[ICHIJO]
Hmm.
[YONAGA]
Um... Hey, Sana?
[SANA]
Ah?
Well, it's just. your hair.
I see you cut it.
Oh. Yeah.
It's so short, at first
I didn't even recognize you.
But I think it looks good.
Really good.
[SANA chuckles]
Maybe you should get a bob, too.
[ASAHI]
Um, get a what?
What's a bob?
So they were being held captive
by the same people who had Sana?
That's right.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm?
[ASAHI]
Errors?
[SANA]
Yeah.
Sometimes my power just
activates itself randomly,
like it did earlier.
It doesn't always produce
something when it happens,
but when it does,
I never know what it'll be.
So it's dangerous.
That sounds like
something you should probably
get checked out
sooner than later.
[SANA] Ichijo's looking into it,
but she hasn't had any luck.
[YONAGA]
Hey, um... Sana?
[SANA]
Huh?
[YONAGA] We wanna say sorry
about earlier today.
For running away.
The truth is...
...since everything
that's happened,
we've really missed you.
[YONAGA] More than anything, we
wanted to tell you we're sorry.
You're sorry? But what for?
[ASAHI]
The thing is...
...before we came
to the facility,
some pretty awful stuff
happened to us.
[ASAHI]
We were scared.
That's why we didn't want you
going out into the world.
They've had a rough life.
Those girls were in
police custody before
the research facility
took them in.
Why the police?
They were being
abused by their father.
It was horrific.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm...
[YONAGA pants]
[ASAHI whimpers]
Get away from her right now!
I mean it!
[thud]
[ICHIJO] Back then,
their thoughts and feelings
were so completely intertwined,
they had trouble telling
themselves apart.
Take a good look.
Starting today, this is going to
be your new home.
Pretty big place, isn't it?
The air's nice, too.
Unfortunately, I can't let you
go outside whenever you want to,
but you'll have lots of
studying to do,
And somewhere to play.
I think you'll like it.
Where would you like to sleep?
We can give you
separate rooms if you want.
[TWINS]
We want to stay together.
[laughs]
Got it.
You're in perfect sync, huh?
That reminds me.
You'll need these.
I'm sorry, but it's very
difficult to tell you apart,
so could you remind me
who is who, again?
I want to make sure
I give you the right ID cards.
Tell me, which of you is older
and which is younger?
[TWINS]
Hmm.
[KITO]
Hmm?
[ASAH] All right, then.
Looks like I'm the older sister.
[YONAGA] Oh. That makes
me the younger one, then.
So, my name's Yonaga. Right?
[ASAHI]
That was our new life.
Never leaving the facility,
living there together,
just the two of us.
But then things changed.
[YONAGA]
Because, one day, we met you.
We played with you,
and it was fun.
We gave you a name, and taught
you most of what we knew.
But not all.
We never told you there was
a world outside the facility.
That's why we're sorry.
[ASAHI]
We did a terrible thing to you.
You deserved to know more.
It wasn't as if
you were our doll.
[YONAGA]
But then you left anyway.
And just like that, our world
was turned upside down.
We never thought everything we
had could disappear so quickly.
But in the blink of an eye,
it was gone.
[ASAHI]
Things are different now.
We've started going to
this American school
that's in Yokosuka.
All of us from the research
facility have been placed
in new homes.
[ASAHI] Ours has a really nice
dorm mother, so that's good.
The language is still
a bit difficult for us,
but we're making friends.
We've even joined clubs.
That's right.
I'm in the badminton club,
and Asahi joined the art club.
[SANA]
Is going to school a lot of fun?
[ASAHI]
Yeah, I guess so.
We're always doing new things,
so that's cool.
[SANA]
Okay, good.
I was worried it would
be dumb and boring.
[YONAGA]
Hey, Sana.
I know a lot has happened,
and things have changed.
But you were the first
real friend we had.
That won't change. Not ever.
[ASAHI]
We're very sorry, Sana.
For everything.
Please forgive us.
[SANA]
Sure!
[ZOROKU]
Hmm.
[SANA]
Okay, we've made up now!
[TWINS]
Hey, hold on!
[SANAE]
Oh, really? That's so nice!
What else did the three
of you talk about?
All different stuff.
Apparently, they've both
joined clubs at their school.
[SANAE]
Yeah, I know.
You already told me that, silly.
[SANA]
Mm. Oh, right.
I did, huh?
Sorry, it's all kind of
a blur right now.
[SANAE]
You must've been really happy.
[SANA]
Yeah, I guess so.
[SANAE]
I'm glad.
It's great you got to see
your friends again.
[SANA]
Hmm...
[SANA groans]
[SANA sobbing]
[SANAE]
Hmm?
[SANA whimpers]
[SANAE]
Are you okay?
[SANA sobs]
[SANAE]
Ah...
[SANA]
Sanae!
[SANAE]
Oh, Sana! What's wrong?
You wanna talk?
[SANA] It's just--
Suddenly, I feel like
I don't understand anything.
[SANAE]
Yeah, that's rough.
You know, back
when I was little,
sometimes I'd suddenly
get really sad
in the middle of the night,
so I'd go and crawl
into Grandpa's futon.
[SANA] The thing is...
I'm not sad or anything.
'Least I don't think.
[SANAE]
Well, that's good.
Earlier, you were so happy
after talking to your friends.
[SANA]
It's hard to explain.
Since I left the research
facility, I felt so weird,
almost like I'm not
myself anymore.
[SANA]
I'm frazzled all the time.
Like somewhere inside,
there's this confused person
who isn't me but
still kind of is.
And that other person
is taking over,
erasing everything I thought
I knew and replacing it
with things that are
fuzzy and unclear.
I want to make it stop,
but I don't know how.
[SANAE]
Hmm.
[SANA]
It was like that today.
The moment I saw the twins,
I felt frazzled,
and I couldn't think
about anything else.
When that happens, I snap
and lose control of myself.
Even my power is acting weird.
[SANA] The outside world
is doing this to me.
I don't know if I can take it!
[SANAE]
I see.
You're starting to understand a
lot of things, little by little,
and that's hard to take in.
[SANA] Hold on. What
are you talking about?
I just told you I don't
understand anything.
[SANAE]
Yeah, I know.
But maybe what you have
to understand is that it's okay
for you not to understand stuff.
[SANA]
Huh?
[SANAE]
Frazzle, frazzle!
[SANA] Hey! Stop that!
What are you doing?
Quit it!
[SANAE]
I love you a whole lot, Sana.
You understand that, don't you?
[SANA]
Get off! And stop teasing me!
I'm serious about
being frazzled!
It's the worst feeling ever.
[SANAE]
I'll tell you what.
I know you're upset,
but it's late.
So why don't you come
and stay in my room
for the rest of the night?
[SANA]
I can do that?
[SANAE]
We'll talk more if you want.
You can tell me all about
how frazzled you feel,
and I'll help you if I can.
[ASAHI]
Good morning, Yonaga.
[YONAGA] Morning, Sis.
Guess it's time to get up.
--[ASAHI]
--[YONAGA] Hey!
Take a look at this!
We received an email from Sana!
[ASAHI]
Huh?!
[YONAGA] You must be
pretty relieved, huh, Sis?
[ASAHI]
What? What do you mean?
You were the one who
was worried about her!
[YONAGA]
So were you, and you know it.
[SANA] Is it done?
Did you send the email?
[SANAE] Sure did.
Do you still feel frazzled?
[SANA]
Mm... Let me see.
I think maybe not
so much anymore.
Good, I'm glad.
[laughs]
[SANA] "Sorry I left
the research facility.
You two are my friends."
[SANA] "Let's play together
again. Sana Kashimura."
[SANA]
"The Evil Witch."