[AYUMU]
Okay, well.
I guess I'll just go home.
Okay. See you later.
What is this power?
[HATORI] What am
I supposed to do with it?
I feel like it's draining me.
When I use it, I get so
hungry I can't even think.
I'm so tired I can barely stand.
I don't like what it does to me,
but I don't know how to stop.
[HATORI'S MOM]
Hatori?
[footsteps]
What are you doing sitting
by the door like that?
Your cheeks are so pale.
Are you all right?
[HATORI]
Thank you for asking.
It's nice of you to worry.
What's wrong?
Which "Mom" are you right now?
The same mom I've always been.
What a strange question.
Now, do you wanna
tell me what's wrong?
[HATORI]
I don't know what to do.
I'm scared.
[HATORI'S MOM]
Don't worry.
It'll be all right.
Mama's always here for you.
[HATORI]
I'm sorry, Mom. I'm so sorry.
[HATORI] The little girl
didn't heed the warning
she'd been given, and so
she became an evil witch.
For that, she would
be burned at the stake.
[SANAE humming]
[ASAHI]
Hey, uh...
[YONAGA] We really don't
mind helping, you know.
No. Don't worry about it.
You two are guests, so I'm not
going to put you to work.
Just sit down and relax.
[stomach growling]
Zoroku. Food. [gasps]
[footsteps]
[BOTH gasp]
Where is he?!
Please! Where is he?
Where's Zoroku?
[ZOROKU]
Oh, good. You're up.
Feel okay?
Are you really back
to normal now?
You're not going to go all
weird on me again, are you?
I couldn't handle that.
So something really
did happen, then.
[SANA whimpers]
[ZOROKU]
Hm...?
[cries]
[ZOROKU]
Okay, I'm off.
If anything happens,
call me, okay?
If nothing happens,
call me anyway!
I will, calm down.
I'll be working late today.
If you need anything,
you know how to reach me.
[SANA]
Be careful out there!
[ZOROKU]
Yep.
Okay. I'm pretty cold.
Why don't we go back inside?
All right.
Hey! What are you doing here?
--She's kidding.
--Unreal!
[SANAE] Your friends
were worried about you,
so they wanted to wait here
until you woke up
to make sure that you were okay.
These two were almost
as concerned as I was.
Is that really true?
[ASAHI]
Yeah, well...
It would've been a waste
to turn around and go back
after coming all this way.
Can't you be nice for once?
[SANAE] Tell you what,
I'll go ahead and start cooking.
If you want, you girls
can have a nice bath.
Maybe get the futons
set up, too.
Sure, that sounds good.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Since when do you
take baths, Sana?
[SANA]
Is it really that weird?
[BOTH]
Well, yeah!
I mean, you never used to
take them at the facility!
[SANA] Things change.
I take baths sometimes now.
It's no big deal.
[SANAE]
Wow! Epic twin cuteness!
Every word was in sync!
If you want to know a secret,
Sana's recently discovered
a hidden love of bubble baths.
[BOTH gasp]
[SANAE] She says it's like
soaking in a big, fluffy cloud.
[TWINS]
Ah...
[SANAE]
And that's not all.
She enjoys hot springs
bath salts, too.
Her favorite is--
Okay, that's enough!
[SANAE] Would you like to
bathe before we eat or after?
Either way is fine, so just tell
me what you prefer.
Oh, we're not picky.
We do normally like to
bathe together, though.
Aw! Well, you're welcome
to share. We don't mind.
Idiot! You didn't
have to tell her that!
[YONAGA]
Sorry.
[SANA]
Wait.
Why did you say something about
setting up futons earlier?
Why do you think?
They need a place to sleep.
Grandpa figured you would want
them to stay over for the night.
[SANA]
Stay over?
Like, until tomorrow?
That's the idea.
[screams]
Wow, really?! That's awesome!
I can't believe it...
Knew you'd be excited.
[screams]
Okay, hop to it!
Are you ready to
show these ladies
where the towels are, Sana?
Yeah! I'm in charge of
the towels now, you know!
For everyone!
Oh, would you like some juice?
Or, there's milk, too!
You have to drink with
one hand on your waist.
Otherwise, you're
doing it all wrong.
[SANA hums]
[ASAHI gasps]
I can't believe she's actually
washing herself by hand.
Without using her
power even a little.
You guys should do it, too.
You're supposed to wash yourself
before getting in the bath.
That's how it's done.
See how much I've learned?
[SANA] Then, you sink in
up to your shoulders
and stay there until
you've counted to 100.
They call it a
"crow's quick bath."
But, why?
What do crows have
to do with anything?
Obviously, crows bathe fast
so they named it that.
Dry your hair thoroughly,
or you could catch cold.
[TWINS laugh]
[stomach growls]
[SANAE]
Are you done in the bath?
Dinner's on the table!
[ALL gasp]
[GROUP]
Thank you for the food!
That was delicious!
So fast!
[YONAGA]
Sana is actually washing dishes.
It's not just the
dishes, either.
She also looks after the
flowers, does laundry,
and takes out the trash
when it's her turn
on the chore wheel.
[BOTH]
Wow!
[vibrating]
[SANA]
Done.
[SANAE]
Hello, Grandpa. What's up?
[SANA]
Uh?
Okay, no problem.
[SANA]
Is that Zoroku?
[SANAE]
Yep, everything's fine here.
Hey, what's he saying?
Can I talk to him?
[SANAE]
Just a second, okay, Grandpa?
I'm going to pass
the phone to Sana.
Here.
Hi, Zoroku!
Yeah. I'm feeling
a lot better now.
No. Why would you think
we'd be fighting?
Well, we're not. I swear!
And I haven't used
my power, either.
Mm-hm! Yeah, I ate plenty.
And don't worry, I'll brush
my teeth before bed!
[GIRLS laughing]
Look at that!
They're squished together
like giant marshmallows.
How're we all gonna fit in here?
[YONAGA]
Oh, whatever.
We'll make it work.
[ASAHI sighs]
You know, uh, it's late.
We should quiet down.
Get some sleep, maybe.
The whole point of a slumber
party is to have fun.
But we could get in trouble!
That's weird.
It's like you switched
personalities.
[YONAGA]
Uh?
How so?
--[chuckles]
--[gasps]
[TWINS laughing]
It's time for some
tickle payback!
Tickle, tickle!
Sana, come help
me get my revenge!
[SANA]
I have no idea what's going on.
Just get over here already!
[ASAHI]
No! Not there!
[SANA] I don't get it,
but sure, I'll help!
[GIRLS laughing]
Shh!
[YONAGA, ASAHI whimper]
Uh. Right.
[SANAE] Oh! Oh, my gosh,
that was too sweet!
A twin sister tickle session!
I wish I could've joined in!
[SANA]
I hate this. He's late.
Um. I didn't know being a
florist was such hard work.
[SANA]
It's not that hard, usually.
Sometimes it is, I guess.
But, well, with what
that girl did...
It's strange not being able
to remember what happened.
There's a Dream of Alice out
there who can control people.
Were you scared, Sana?
I was terrified.
It was so awful,
what she did to everyone.
You all just stopped moving.
And I was alone.
[ASAHI]
I have to wonder...
[YONAGA
...if she wasn't scared, too.
[gasps] There's no way!
She's too evil to be scared.
I'll never forgive her.
How can you feel bad for her
after what she did to you?
I was really excited about
you guys coming over.
So today, Zoroku was supposed
to get off work early.
He's still there,
and it's all her fault.
I hate her.
She makes me feel frazzled.
[TWINS exhale]
[SANA gasps]
[door opens]
[ZOROKU]
Huh?
[SANA]
Zoroku.
What are you doing down here?
Shouldn't you be sleeping?
[SANA]
I was asleep. I woke up.
[ZOROKU]
Oh. Hey, cut that out.
You're home for the night,
aren't you?
You're not going anywhere else?
That's right.
Not going anywhere.
You shouldn't cling so much.
You'll start to
smell like cigarettes,
and you know how
Sanae'll feel about that.
[SANA]
Too bad!
Fine, give me a second.
At least let me wash the
smoke smell off of a me.
Are your friends asleep already?
[SANA]
Mm-hm.
Promise me that you won't leave.
And that you won't
turn all weird again.
[ZOROKU]
I told you, I'm not leaving.
Now, come on. Let go.
[BOTH laugh]
She really has changed.
I've never seen her
so clingy before.
[YONAGA]
Yeah.
[BOTH laugh]
[SANA snoring]
[SANA grunts]
[gasps]
[BOTH]
Thanks so much for having us.
You're welcome to visit
again sometime.
[TWINS]
Great!
I had a really good time!
Thanks for coming!
You'll stay over
again sometime, right?
You promise?
[BOTH]
We'll be back, we promise!
I should go.
There's a lot to do.
Where, the shop?
Aren't you usually
off today, though?
[ZOROKU] I need to redo
the arrangements that wilted
during the confusion yesterday.
I won't be too long.
Shame he has to do
all that work over.
[inaudible]
He's leaving because of her.
I'm gonna get her good for this!
Hello, dear.
Hello. Is Hatori here?
She's upstairs in her room.
[HATORI'S MOM]
Here you go.
Oh. Thank you.
[HATORI'S MOM]
Well, you girls have fun.
[footsteps]
We will, Mom. Thanks.
[door creaks]
[AYUMU] So, um, you haven't
been at school lately.
And I'm not planning
to go back, either.
[AYUMU]
Uh?
I'm sorry, but you know it'll
be better if I stay away.
No, I don't know that!
And would you stop apologizing?
You didn't ask
for this stuff to happen!
The police have come by
here a few times now.
[gasps]
It's okay, though.
I made them leave.
It wasn't even difficult.
Nobody can touch me.
An evil witch can do anything.
[HATORI] I know what
I said, but I'm sorry.
I won't be
running away, after all.
But why?
I need to stay.
I realized my mom and dad would
be better off with me here.
Maybe I should have
told you this before,
but it's been bad.
They've been fighting
for a long time.
And all because of me.
Because I couldn't live up
to my mom's expectations.
When I use my magic,
things go back to
the way they used to be.
They're finally happy again.
[inaudible]
[HATORI]
But once the magic wears off,
the fighting just
starts back up.
I have to stay here forever.
It's the only way
they'll be happy.
It's fine. Even if it is a lie.
[gasping]
[cries]
[AYUMU]
She's wrong! I know she is.
There has to be
a way to fix this.
I don't want to give up.
I don't want to accept
there's nothing I can do!
I'll help her.
Somehow...
[door creaks]
[ZOROKU]
I'm back.
Welcome home, Grandpa.
Hey, Zoroku!
[SANA humming]
What's Sana working on?
No idea.
She's been at it a while.
Most of the day, I think.
[ZOROKU exhales]
Ha, ha! Those two aren't
going to know what hit them!
[SANA laughs]
[hums]
[chimes]
[NAITO] This is the girl
we're here to see.
Hatori Shikishima,
age nine, in third grade.
She's an only child
living with both parents.
The security cameras made
it easy to identify her,
but it's still hard to believe.
[HATORI'S MOM]
Yes?
[BOTH]
Uh!
This is Yamada.
We spoke on the phone.
[HATORI'S MOM]
We did?
Uh! I'm sorry, are you
Hatori Shikishima's mother?
I'd like to speak with
you about something
concerning your daughter
if you have a moment.
[HATORI gasps]
[NORIKO]
Is Hatori home?
Maybe we can talk to you both.
[NORIKO]
Um, hello?
[HATORI'S MOM]
What's this about?
Is my daughter in
trouble or something?
No, ma'am.
We just wanted to talk.
[NAITO] Well, glad we
got that taken care of.
I guess it's time to head back.
Let's go.
Uh! Wait.
What did we get "taken care of"?
Uh. You know, it was
that thing we had to do.
Yeah, right, that thing.
Let's get some food.
I'm starvin', here.
[NORIKO] Fine. But I don't
want beef bowls again.
Really, would it kill you to let
me choose where we eat for once?
It's only fair.
[NAITO]
Yeah, sure, whatever.
[NORIKO yelps]
[NAITO grunts]
Aw... Give a girl some
warning, would you?
Why'd ya stop like that?
[NAITO grunts]
[NORIKO]
Ah...
This is the fifth time. Damn.
Hey, I think we've
been had, Yamada.
Huh?
[gasps]
That girl's really something.
She got us good.
The only people who can
get inside that house
are the ones she allows.
She's the gatekeeper.
The power to control others.
So it's really true, then.
If she'd only
let us talk to her,
we might be able
to help her out.
And this girl's
going to need help.
With that kinda power,
there's no way she can get
through this on her own.
[AYUMU]
Who was that girl the other day?
The magic she used
looked just like Hatori's.
[inaudible]
[AYUMU] If I can find her and
convince her to talk to me,
maybe she can help.
[AYUMU] Hatori's magic had
never been broken before,
but somehow that
girl managed it.
Where did this power come from?
Will she ever be rid of it?
If I could only find that girl.
I'm sorry, Ayu, I really am.
But please don't
ever come back here.
You're kidding me!
It has to be this way.
If you came back,
I might end up hurting you.
[AYUMU]
I don't believe that!
You would never hurt me!
I trust you, Hatori.
I'm not afraid!
[HATORI]
Don't you see? I'm like a bear.
A bear?
If a bear leaves its home--
if it attacks somebody--then
it can never be returned
to the mountains
where it belongs.
The bear has to be killed.
When I was little, I thought it
was cruel to punish an animal
just for doing what
was in its nature.
But now I understand.
You see? The same
is true for me.
I can't be among people anymore.
I'm sorry. I really am.
But don't come back.
[AYUMU grunts]
[AYUMU]
I won't accept that! Never!
[MAN A] Hm? You say you're
lookin' for a foreign girl?
"Young and blonde's" not
much of a description.
What? A blonde girl?
There are plenty of those
coming through here every day.
Thanks anyway.
Sorry, kid.
[AYUMU sighs]
Maybe this was a stupid idea.
Tons of people live around here,
and it's not like I can
ask for her by name.
[GIRL B] I think I'll try
something new today.
[GIRL A] I'll just have
the usual, thanks.
[GIRL B]
Boring!
[AYUMU]
The shop we stopped at...
That was wrong.
We shouldn't have
used her power like that.
Or at all.
[chimes]
[gasps]
[CHESHIRE CAT growls]
[AYUMU gasping]
[AYUMU screaming]
[gasps]
[crash]
[AYUMU groaning]
Ow... Ow, ow, ow!
[sighs] Wait. That's weird.
No pain.
[AYUMU]
How did I get down here?
[gasps]
[AYUMU]
Huh? Hey!
What's happening?
Where'd that hole go?
[SANA laughing]
I finally found you!
[SANA laughs]
[AYUMU gasping]
Heh!
[gasps]
[SANA laughing]
[AYUMU gasping]
[SANA grunts]
You evil, frazzling meanie!
I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
[AYUMU gasping]
[SANA]
"The Little Queen."