[NAITO]
I'm sorry. I was careless.
I had our people watching your
house and the surrounding area,
but it was stupid of me not to
make certain that
this place was secure, too.
I mean, it's not
like I expected them
to take her while she
was in the bathroom.
But I should have
been more careful.
My fault...
I'm the one who brought Sana
here and put her in danger.
[NAITO]
Don't say that. It's okay.
This isn't your fault, I swear.
Ichijo and our colleague Yamada
are on their trail right now.
They'll find her
before too long.
You're sure? Really?
[ZOROKU]
Calm down. Panicking won't help.
But Grandpa...
She'll be okay, you'll see.
[SANAE sighs]
[NAITO]
He's right about that.
She should be safe enough.
She's valuable to
the people who took her.
I don't think they'll
be quick to harm her.
But you don't know.
It's all right.
[NAITO sighs]
'Kay...
[MINNIE]
Do you understand now?
Shall I spell it out for you?
[SANA whimpers]
If you struggle or disobey,
I will swiftly lose
what patience I have,
and you will die.
If it meant
seeing his face again,
I would do absolutely anything.
[car horns honking]
I don't get why
anyone would want to live
someplace so noisy.
[door clacks]
[KITO]
Hmm?
[DRIVER A]
Got the supplies.
[CLEO] I wanna go home
and play video games.
Our part's over, right?
Yes. We can leave the rest
for Minnie C. to handle.
I'm sure she'll bring the
Red Queen home to us soon.
You all did
an excellent job today.
If you get hungry
before we make it back,
there are plenty of snacks for--
[CLEO]
I'm sick of sweets.
Can we go? We're done here.
[YONAGA]
When this is over,
things will go back
to normal, right?
She'll come home and be happy?
Yeah. Back to normal, sure.
[SANA whimpers]
I have to admit,
I expected much more from you.
You once commanded the
principles of space itself.
If this is all you can do
in the outside world,
you truly are no
more than a child.
[MINNIE] You managed to
obtain a body, learn language,
and acquire emotions.
Then you fled the facility
for the outside world,
where you could
pretend to be human.
And yet, do you see how easily I
was able to render you helpless?
[SANA]
Pretend to be human?
What does she mean?
I don't understand.
Or am I wrong?
Have you deluded
yourself into believing
you're a real human girl?
[SANA gasps]
[MINNIE]
Is that it, Red Queen?
[ZOROKU] Will you tell me
why they want her so badly?
I called you because
she was obviously being
mistreated at
this facility place,
and I thought that you'd
be able to help her.
But now, it's clear that
something big is going on here
and you and your people
are involved somehow, too.
Sorry, state secret.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm?!
[laughs]
Gotcha, I'm only kidding.
Think of it as something
of a territorial dispute.
There are two officials high-up
in the government who have
differing opinions
on a particular matter.
I work for one of them, so I was
sent in my official capacity.
I know you're
not telling me everything.
Like who the girl
actually is, for example.
[NAITO]
Hmm... Well, to be honest,
I'm not sure you'll
believe me when I tell you.
But you see, the fact is,
in all likelihood--
Sana's not a little girl, or
even human for that matter.
[BOTH gasp]
Whatever you are, there's
one thing we know for sure.
You're not human.
In fact, 13 years ago,
when you first appeared
beneath the research facility,
you couldn't even be
considered a living thing.
[SANA whimpers]
You were just an
unknown entity absorbing
the thoughts and reactions of
the living beings around you.
You took what you read in others
and turned it into reality.
Everything you seem
to be now--your appearance,
your ego, your
emotions, your speech--
Those were all cards that an
ownerless Mirror Gate
created by copying
them from humans.
Have you forgotten that?
[SANA]
That's a lie!
I'm Sana. I'm real!
[MINNIE] Do you see now
why you must not leave
the research facility?
You can't live in the outside
world with real people.
It's better for
everybody involved this way.
Wonderland is the
only place you belong.
Now, quiet down.
It's time to take you back home.
[NAITO] Sana and the others
who have similar powers
are referred to as
Dreams of Alice.
We have reason to believe
that, before long,
many more people will
have abilities like theirs.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm...
[NAITO] This might
all sound like something
out of a storybook,
but the ethical challenges
it poses are real.
We may have to reconsider
our definition of humanity.
Can our society learn
to accept beings like her,
who possess near infinite power?
That's a question
we'll be faced with soon.
The people I work with believe
such acceptance is possible.
However, those on
the other side disagree.
So, does that help clear
things up for you a little?
I suppose it does.
[NAITO] We've been
working behind the scenes
for a while now,
doing what we can.
But then we learned that the
girl who's at the center
of all this had ended
up with none other
than my old buddy Roku.
And I would have been
a complete idiot not to make use
of that opportunity.
Oh, yeah? How?
Well, to determine
whether regular humans
can coexist with
somebody like Sana.
It sounded like a good idea.
[ZOROKU] You never have
been one to worry too much
about how your actions
affect other people.
Heh. Sorry.
[ZOROKU] Hmph. You and I can
talk some more about that later.
First, we need to get
the girl back home.
Sanae.
The two of you get along
pretty well, don't you?
[SANAE]
Yes. We do.
Okay. She can
stay with us, then.
I... Well, uh-- I
don't mind if she stays.
[SANAE] But Grandpa,
I wish you wouldn't do that.
You always make
decisions this way.
On your own,
without talking to me.
Like before, y'know.
When you told me
Sana was at our place.
It was fine, but I wish you had
given me a say in the matter.
I do like Sana, but...
...you tend to do things without
asking how I feel about them.
I do?
Uh-huh, all the time.
It makes me feel unimportant.
Please, Grandpa.
Just talk to me more.
That's especially important
if we're going to be
a family of three.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm...
Please try.
Yeah. Sure. I will.
[SANAE giggles]
Thanks, Grandpa.
[NAITO]
Hmm.
[MINNIE] Nice as it's been,
our chat's over.
We still have a ways to go.
And I would prefer
to have you quiet.
[SANA whimpers]
[SANA] Is she right about
me not being human?
Is that why I wasn't allowed
in the outside world?
Why they kept me locked up
in the research facility?
[SANA]
Because... I'm a monster?
I'm not, though. I'm not!
Right?
This stuff will slow down
your mind and your body.
We don't want to
knock you out altogether.
Unlike most people,
you're more dangerous
when you're completely
unconscious.
Ah... Disgusting.
[WOMAN]
Hello. What are you doing here?
It's sort of against
the rules, you see.
For us to be talking.
[SANA] I feel like I've met you,
but I'm not sure when.
Who are you?
Who am I? Hmm. Let's see...
Why don't you think of me
as a really cool lady
you don't yet know?
Huh? You have talked
to me before, though.
At the research facility.
Oh? Are you sure about that?
Heh. You're flat.
[WOMAN]
Uh...
You're a grown up,
but Sanae has
bigger boobs than you.
I hope you don't ever
forget you said that.
You'll find it less funny later.
--[SANA] Hey.
--[WOMAN] Hmm?
I just found out I may not be
a human like I thought I was.
I think I may be monster.
Don't worry, you're not
the only one confused.
Most people don't know
what they really are.
Including me.
I'm still searching
for that answer.
I probably shouldn't
tell you this,
but I was actually very lucky
when I was younger.
I had people around me
who were wiser than I was
and were willing to help me.
I'm sure you have someone, too.
Maybe what you should
do now is call their name.
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Hey. Did you
just hear something?
[NAITO]
Are you kidding?! Look!
Above you!
[ZOROKU]
Hmm? The hell's that thing?
I think I know.
[ZOROKU gasps]
It's Sana! She sent it!
Save her, Grandpa!
[ZOROKU]
Huh?!
[SANA]
Zo... roku...
Huh?!
[SANA whimpers]
[ZOROKU]
Hmm? Hm! Hey!
[MINNIE gasps]
[ZOROKU grunts]
What the--?
Sana! Are you okay?
What happened?
Can you hear me?
[SANA] I think that's the first
time he's called me Sana.
[ZOROKU]
Are you one of them?
One of the people who have
been abusing this little girl?
I really shouldn't
be surprised, should I?
After all,
you only cause trouble.
[ZOROKU]
Whoever or whatever you are.
I'm not messing around.
I'm not gonna let
you get away with this.
I hate crooked stuff!
Oh? Is that so?
And just who are you?
[ZOROKU]
I am a florist.
I may not be strong,
but I don't give up easily.
Hey!
Where'd all your
energy go, Sana?
You said you could do anything
just by thinking about it.
So what are you still doing
here with this woman?
[groans]
Sana...!
Get back home now!
You remember that so-called
friend of mine, Naito?
Well, he's going to help you.
[SANA whimpers]
Don't worry about me.
I'll be okay. Hurry. Go now!
What must I do to
get you to stop talking?
[ZOROKU]
You--
[SANA squeals]
[ZOROKU]
Sana!
Damn you!
[yells, grunts]
[SANA whimpers]
[MINNIE]
Listen closely.
If you try anything at all,
Red Queen,
the punishment will be
far worse than a hurt leg.
and next time,
you won't be the one I shoot.
[ZOROKU]
Sana!
Understand? You won't
get another warning.
[ZOROKU]
Your leg! Oh, god! Sana!
[SANA]
No! No more!
It wasn't supposed
to be like this!
All I wanted was
to see the outside world...
This is all my fault.
I pretended to be a human and
called Zoroku here to help me.
Why did I drag him
into this? Why?
It's over... Time to let go...
[MINNIE grunts]
[gasps]
[SANA]
That's enough. I understand.
Leave him alone.
Don't do anything to Zoroku.
Hey! I've got you.
Guess she
finally ran out of energy.
Your leg.
You're bleeding badly.
There's not much time.
[gasps]
[MINNIE]
Her power is unbelievable.
She did more than
just erase all evidence
that she'd been wounded,
she rewrote multiple aspects
of her current reality.
I've got a location for Sana!
She's on the Shuto Expressway
headed toward Oi Futo, fast.
[NAITO] Roger. I've got
a contact in Port Authority
who'll let me know
if he sees anything suspicious.
Ichijo, did you get that?
[ICHIJO]
Yes! I'll head that way.
[NAITO]
Good luck.
There, you see?
Nothing to worry about anymore.
[SANAE]
Um, right.
I should head out, too,
in case they need me.
Home is probably the
best place for you now.
I'll get someone
to give you a ride.
Wait here, okay?
[NAITO]
Hmm?
[SANAE]
Um. I'm sorry...
But do you think
I could come, too?
[SANA sobs]
I'm sorry, Zoroku...
You were right not to
trust me... I'm a monster...
I'm sorry... I'm so, so sorry...
It's no big deal.
Don't get all worked up.
[SANA whimpers]
I'm sorry!
Full name: Zoroku Kashimura.
Age: 72.
Owner of the flower shop
Kashimura Floral.
Your family consists of one
granddaughter who's in
her second year of high school.
You know a lot about me, huh?
I'm afraid I'll need
you to accompany us
for a while, preferably quietly.
[ZOROKU] How about
you tell me who you are?
[MINNIE]
My name is Miriam C. Tachibana.
I'm a special consultant
on a state project.
One the Japanese and
American governments
are working on together.
[ZOROKU] A project involving
the Dreams of Alice, right?
[MINNIE]
Aren't you well-informed?
Yes, we're studying the
Dreams of Alice with the goal
of developing a way to
artificially reproduce
their powers. Ultimately,
our intention is to
use what we learn to build
a new energy system.
If it's successful,
our project will
benefit all of humanity.
[ZOROKU] You think you can
justify locking up a child,
testing her, dissecting her,
who knows what else,
because in the end,
it's a benefit to humanity?
[chuckles] Oh, a fan of
science fiction, are you?
No, we're not
going to dissect her.
However, you should know
that she is not a human,
let alone the innocent child
you suppose her to be.
[ZOROKU growls]
[MINNIE] The Red Queen
is something else entirely.
Not a person,
but an unknown being
with the ability to
mimic humanity.
[ZOROKU] Hah. None of that
makes any sense.
She looks like
an ordinary little girl.
[MINNIE] Imagine a weapon
of mass destruction
adopted an
artificial personality
and the form of a young girl.
[SANA groans]
Knowing that,
would you be so eager
--to leap to its defense?
--Huh?
A monster of untold power
is attempting
to insinuate itself into
our society in disguise.
What?
[MINNIE]
Tell me.
Once she came into your lives,
have you or your granddaughter
found yourselves
in mortal danger?
Sana! You don't
have to listen to her!
Lady, everything
you're saying is ridicu--
[SANA]
That's enough!
Please, Zoroku, that's enough...
I think the things she
said might be true.
I really am a monster.
It would explain a lot
of things about me.
--Sana...
--I'm ready to accept it now.
But I don't want you
to see what I really am.
It would probably
make you hate me.
Well, that's if you
don't hate me already.
[chuckles weakly]
I'll be okay.
I don't want you or Sanae
to end up in danger again
because of me.
Don't say that.
[SANA] All this happened
because I wanted to be human.
That's not fair to you.
It'll be better for you
if I'm not around.
I'm so sorry, for everything.
Really. I'll go back
to the research facility.
Thank you so much, though.
The food was really yummy.
Ichijo, I've got a helicopter
ready. You coming?
[ICHIJO]
I'll go on my own.
It'll be faster that way.
[NORIKO] Oh, wow! You're,
like, seriously amazing!
My contact was able to
find out which boat they're on.
Ichijo will have them back safe
and sound in no time.
Oh. Good.
[NAITO]
It'll all work out.
I bet your grandpa's lecturing
the kidnapper as we speak.
The first words out of
his mouth were probably,
"I hate crooked stuff!"
[laughs]
That memory.
[ZOROKU]
What're you making there?
Can't you tell? They're graves.
[SANAE] I've thought back
to that conversation a lot
over the years, but I've
never been able to recall
exactly what he said.
Till now.
[NAITO]
Hmm?
Before, when
he was talking about
how Sana might become
a part of our family.
I had this feeling.
It was strange
but familiar, too.
like something
tightening in my chest.
You know?
[NAITO]
Hmm.
[SANAE] I think that's what
helped me remember.
Suddenly, Grandpa's words
started coming back to me.
What he said after my parents'
funeral was so comforting.
I felt like everything
would be okay.
It's okay.
Listen, even if it
turns out she's right,
and you're not human,
what does it matter?
Don't give up on yourself, Sana.
[SANA whimpers]
We're going to go
home and figure everything out.
[SANA]
Huh...?
[ZOROKU]
Your name is Miriam, right?
You want me to
believe this little girl
isn't a human being,
but what the hell do you
know about humanity?
You shot a child without
a second thought.
Are you human?
I did what I had to.
That's not the issue here.
You're right
about her being dangerous,
I'll give you that.
The second I take my eyes
off her, she's causing trouble.
At her best,
she's still a nuisance.
That's okay.
Everybody's got flaws,
and she's no different.
But she knows she's not perfect,
and she's trying to improve.
That's what matters.
She's no monster.
She can be nice
if she's well fed.
In her own clumsy way,
she worries about others,
and she's
surprisingly intuitive.
And while she has
caused ten kinds of trouble,
she's never once done
something with malicious intent.
Whoever or whatever Sana is,
she's got a good heart.
That's sweet.
But your personal feelings about
her are completely irrelevant.
You're unqualified to
understand a being like her,
--much less do anything--
--[ZOROKU] Stop right there.
I've heard enough from you.
If there's
one thing I know for sure,
it's that nobody in
this world is perfect.
We lean on each other to get by
because there are some things
you can't do alone,
no matter how smart
or how capable you are.
Isn't that true for you, too?
Look, even if
this girl is some kind of
unknown life form like you say,
that doesn't mean she has
to be locked up like a criminal.
Do you honestly believe
coexistence isn't possible?
[sighs]
[SANA grunts]
But what if she is right?
What if I am a monster?
You can't really want
someone like me around.
I'll cause trouble,
maybe even put you in danger.
You and Sanae both.
That's beside the point.
You deserve to be with
people who will help you
when you need it most,
no matter who or what you are.
[SANA whimpers]
[ZOROKU]
Don't give up, Sana.
Trust me.
We'll figure all this out.
Don't think for a second
that I'm going to let you
go back to that place.
You left to see
the outside world
and find help for your friends.
Then that's what you should do.
Stay away from these people.
They're crooked.
And you know how much
I hate crooked stuff.
[sobs]
You're crazy, right?
Maybe.
--[crashing]
--[SANA gasps]
[grunts]
[ZOROKU gasps]
[ICHIJO]
Sorry it took me so long.
I came as fast as I could.
I'm agent Shizuku Ichijo,
with the Cabinet Information
Research Office.
If you're all finished up
here, I'd like you two
to come with me.
[SANA]
"A Home to Return To."