[KITO] Target appears
to be heading south.
Her footprints were found
approximately 400 meters south
of our current location.
All vehicles are
searching the area.
I'll apprise you as new
information becomes available.
[SURVEILLANCE A]
Director.
The target has
moved out of range
of our surveillance cameras.
Then we'll have
to borrow government
and police cameras as well.
[NORIKO growls]
Damn it! Too slow!
Too damn slow!
[SANA pants]
[KITO]
Target appears to have left
the research facility's
surveillance area.
We're attempting to track
her using street cameras,
but pinpointing her
location may take time.
If the situation
changes on your end,
contact me immediately.
Understood?
[DRIVER A]
Roger.
--May I ask, sir?
--[KITO] Hmm?
Is it possible she jumped
further than we
anticipated she would?
You didn't assume
I limited her calorie intake
at dinner simply for
the fun of it, did you?
I plan to get some
interesting data today.
I wanna see how
far the Queen can go
on the amount of
fuel I allowed her.
This should be fun.
[SANA pants]
[NORIKO]
All right! Now we're talking!
Ugh. Not again!
[groans] This is exactly why
I requested a bigger budget!
[SURVEILLANCE B] Target
located on the national highway,
500 meters southeast.
This is the best image
we can get with
a street surveillance camera.
All vehicles,
move to form a perimeter
around the target's location.
Car four, proceed
directly to the target.
She may have one jump left
in her, but don't worry.
She won't be able to go far.
[NORIKO]
Yes! Analysis complete!
Sending coordinates now!
[DRIVER A]
Car four here.
Minnie C. is heading
toward the target.
[KITO]
Roger.
You can hold
your position for now.
[SANA]
So cold...
Is everything out here...
cold and wet...?
[MIRIAM]
Hello there, Red Queen.
Just where do you
think you're going?
I'm leaving. Stay away from me!
[MIRIAM] Why don't you set
your stubbornness aside
and return to where
it's nice and warm?
[SANA gasps]
No!
[MIRIAM] Come now.
Everyone is waiting for you.
[SANA]
Open!
[SANA gasps]
There, you see?
Your foolish flight has
exhausted all your energy.
Wonderland is the
only place you belong.
It's time to accept that.
[MIRIAM]
Who are you?
That's a surprise.
[SANA groans]
[ICHIJO]
106!
[SURVEILLANCE A]
She appears to be resisting.
[SURVEILLANCE B] As to be
expected from the Red Queen.
I'm just impressed she
had enough power left.
[KITO]
No.
[SURVEILLANCE B]
Huh?
That's not her fighting.
It's someone else.
[ICHIJO]
You need to jump.
[SANA]
Huh...?
[ICHIJO] Visualize the
largest town you can.
Go there and do whatever you
have to to cause a commotion.
Who are you? What do you want?
Questions for another day.
What?!
[KITO]
What happened?
I don't know, sir.
Maybe a lightning
strike shorted our feed.
[SURVEILLANCE C] We'll switch to
another channel and reboot.
Lightning, huh?
Okay! There we go!
[DRIVER A gasps]
[SURVEILLANCE A]
Restoring monitors.
[KITO]
Where's the target?
[SURVEILLANCE B]
I don't see her.
[SURVEILLANCE C]
Nothing there, either.
[MIRIAM]
Tachibana here.
[KITO]
Hm?
[MIRIAM] Capture of the
Red Queen has failed.
There was interference.
[KITO]
Who was it?
[MIRIAM]
I don't know.
A female ability-user
I've never seen.
She gave the Red Queen
food and told her to jump
to a large town and
cause a commotion.
[KITO]
Listen up.
I want all cars except
car four to expand the search
to the metropolitan area.
[DRIVERS]
Roger.
[KITO] Do whatever it takes.
We need to pick up her trail.
[SURVEILLANCE A]
Vehicles have changed course.
[SURVEILLANCE B]
They're heading south,
toward the metro area.
[KITO sighs]
[DRIVER B] Director?
Further pursuit is impossible.
Ah. Why is that?
[DRIVER B]
The bridge... It's just gone.
[KITO] All vehicles, return
to the research facility.
Minne C, I want a detailed
report as soon as you arrive.
Over.
[KITO]
She said to go to a large town
and cause a commotion, but why?
[SANA]
Alice, having drifted in space
for a long time,
began to feel a bit dizzy.
Her legs were shaky
and unstable beneath her.
After a few minutes,
she decided she was
capable of walking again,
and she felt relieved.
She took a moment
to consider her surroundings.
"I shall make my way to the
top of the hill," thought Alice.
"From there, I'll have
a much better view
of that lovely garden."
[CLEO yawns]
I'm sorry that I
had to wake you so early.
You look tired. Feel free
to sleep, if you'd like to.
Okay...
[SURVEILLANCE A]
Target located.
She's in Shinjuku.
Cameras spotted her at 4:57 A.M.
[KITO] Send the relevant footage
to me immediately, please.
[SURVEILLANCE A]
Roger.
[KITO] Well, if she was
looking for a large town,
she certainly found one.
[CROWD chattering]
[ZOROKU]
Well, here's your order.
Excellent work, as I'd expected.
I knew you were the
right man for a job
of this nature, Kashimura.
Is that a fact?
[ZOROKU]
That's a lot.
No more than
you deserve, though.
Consider it a token
of my gratitude.
I took this job because
it was a personal request,
but it goes no further.
I won't get buddy-buddy
with you people.
Careful, old man! Do you know
who you're talkin' to here?!
Did I tell you to speak?!
I'm sorry about that.
My associate can be
a bit hot-headed at times.
I'll accept my fee,
but nothing more than that.
[SAWAKI]
Wait a moment.
You really
are a strange one,
aren't you, Kashimura?
[ZOROKU]
Hmph.
[MINIONS]
Have a good afternoon.
[door bell chimes]
I'll be right with you.
Oh, hi, Kashimura.
Haven't seen you in a while.
[ZOROKU]
A pack of the usual, please.
[CHEN]
You should really quit.
These things'll
kill you, ya know.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, can I talk
to you for a second?
I'm worried about
that little girl over there.
I don't know what
to do about her.
[CHEN] She's been sitting
like that for three hours.
The Red Light
District isn't really
the best place for a child.
[ZOROKU]
Tell the police.
[CHEN sighs] I called,
but they won't do anything.
They never deal with foreigners.
[ZOROKU]
So talk to the shop owner.
I can't! He won't get
involved with the police.
Plus, I'm pretty sure
he's been stealing money
from the donation box.
Not really a stand-up guy.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm...
Hey, kid.
[SANA]
Mm?
--You shouldn't touch something
--That's it, Kashimura!
--unless you're planning to buy.
--You can do it! Way to go!
You look like you're lost. Why
don't you let me take you home?
[SANA]
Uh. You seem familiar.
Have we met before?
[SANA]
Your name is Zoroku Kashimura.
You were born on
June 19th, 1943.
You have one granddaughter
whose name is Sanae.
She's been at training camp
for her high school club
since yesterday.
The first parts make sense,
but I have no idea what a
"club" or a "training camp" is.
I guess we haven't met.
Still, you don't
seem like a bad person.
That settles it.
I think you and I should
come to an arrangement.
And what would that be?
It's simple!
If you help me,
I'll grant you any wish!
What is this, kid?
Something from a comic book?
Well, sorry, but I don't know
much about that stuff.
Uh. If you don't want
to help me, then fine!
Just say no! You don't
have to make fun of me!
I'm not making
fun of you at all.
I just have no clue
what you're talking about.
[SANA whimpers]
Forget it!
What the heck was that?
It's like she just up and
vanished into thin air!
Please tell me you have some
idea what's going on here.
[ZOROKU]
None at all.
[SANA]
This is bad.
I don't have much power left.
There's no choice.
I'll have to go with
that man from the store.
[VENDING MACHINE VOICE A]
Thank you for your business.
Have a nice day.
--[SANA] Hello again.
--[ZOROKU] Hmm?
Were you really serious about
not making a deal with me?
[ZOROKU] Want to tell me
how you got in my car?
[SANA]
That's not important right now.
So, kid, do you have a name?
Where's home?
I don't have a home.
[ZOROKU sighs]
So, what do you say?
Do we have a deal or not?
If you say yes, I'll grant
any wish you want, I swear.
[ZOROKU] Is this how
you always behave
when you're asking
for something?
Being pushy and disrespectful
won't get you far in life.
[SANA]
Hesitate, and you'll die.
--What?
--Look in front of you.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm?
Where did that come from?!
Just get us out of here!
It's not over.
[ASAHI growls]
I can't believe I missed!
I'm not sure about this...
Don't you think we're
taking it a bit too far?
[ASAHI]
Shoot, Yonaga!
I dunno...
[ASAHI] Don't argue!
Just take the shot!
[gasps]
Okay, gimme a sec.
If she won't
change her mind,
I'll just have to do
my best to miss.
Who are those people?
Twin sisters sent to follow me.
The younger can call a bow,
and the older can call
anything with a chain.
Like the wrecking ball,
or the bike they're riding now.
But bikes aren't on chains.
[SANA]
They have them.
[ZOROKU]
Oh, right.
[BOTH scream]
[SANA]
Don't slow down.
They'll be on us
again before long.
[SANA screams]
[SANA whimpers]
Hey, what are you doing?
What'd you stop for?
Get out of my car.
Those two girls are
here because of you, right?
Don't drag a stranger
into your problems.
I don't need that.
You know,
I think I kinda like you.
--You gotta be kidding me here!
--We're being too conspicuous.
--How do I keep missing?!
Ugh, never mind.
Hurry and take another shot!
Okay. Open.
[YONAGA]
I just have to miss.
That shouldn't be
too hard to do.
Okay, what the hell
are you up to now?
It'll be better if I drive.
Oh, yeah, this is much better!
[MAN screams]
Please don't make this
any harder than it has to be.
You did it, Yonaga!
Nicely done!
I'm sorry, Sana...
[MAN A]
What was that?
[WOMAN A] Do you think
we should call the police?
[MAN B]
And an ambulance, too.
[ZOROKU]
What the hell just happened?
[MAN C]
Who are those people?
[WOMAN B]
Are they filming a movie?
[WOMAN C]
So it was all just a stunt?
Ha, ha, ha! There's no
escaping now, Red Queen!
We've got you!
If they wanted to catch me,
they should have sent
somebody stronger than you two.
Oh, you did not
just call us weak!
It's okay, Sis,
take a deep breath.
Please. Come back to the
research facility with us.
I know it can be scary
sometimes, and the tests
they conduct aren't
always pleasant,
but we can't live in the outside
world like regular people.
We don't belong here.
[SANA]
That's a lie!
I won't be fooled anymore.
And I'm through with
being a lab rat.
You hear me?
I'm gonna destroy that place!
No. You can't do that!
You don't know
what you're talking about.
Stop being an idiot!
Do it now. Shoot her!
[YONAGA]
Huh...?
[SANA]
I won't go back.
Sana, please!
I don't want to do this...
I'm sorry!
--[ASAHI] Ow! Ow!
--You little fools.
What gives you the right to
point a dangerous weapon
like that at somebody?
[TWINS whimpering]
[ALL scream]
[SANA grunts]
[YONAGA whines]
[ASAHI yells]
[GIRLS whimper]
[SANA] Hey! What do you
think you're doing?!
That's the question
you should be asking yourself.
What are you doing,
behaving like this
in the middle of the city?!
Do you know how many
people could have been hurt
by one wrong move in your
nonsensical game of tag?!
Take a look at all
the damage you've caused!
This isn't a video game.
It's real!
And as for the two of you.
--[TWINS whimper]
--Um, yes?
[ZOROKU] What's this about?
You have a problem with me?
No, we don't, sir.
No, of course not.
No problem at all.
Then listen.
There're boundaries in
life you must respect.
I don't know who you are or
what you've been through,
but old folks and children
walk around this area.
Whether you intended to or not,
you three could have
killed somebody today.
[SANA sighs]
Here's the deal.
The police are going
to be here soon.
You'll go with them
quietly and apologize
for your reckless behavior.
[ZOROKU]
Understood?!
[GIRLS]
Um... yes!
[applause]
[sirens approaching]
[OFFICER A] Okay. Let's
start with something easy.
Why don't you give
me your names?
[TWINS groan]
[OFFICER A]
Hmm...
[OFFICER B]
Hmm.
[OFFICER C]
Okay, first things first.
Maybe you could
tell me your name?
Sure, but could
you do something for me?
[stomach growls]
I'm guessing
you could use a snack.
[MITAKA] You expect me to
believe that ridiculous story?
[ZOROKU] Maybe you should
talk to the other witnesses
at the scene.
I'm betting they'll tell you the
same ridiculous story I am.
[growls]
Fine.
Well, maybe you'd like
to explain these, then.
These photographs show
you leaving Sawaki's office.
The incident today is connected
to your little visit, isn't it?
Are the yakuza in
the habit of materializing
wrecking balls from thin air?
I'm asking the questions here!
I was there to deliver an order,
nothing more than that.
And was it your "delivery"
that caused this mess?
[POLICEMAN A]
Sergeant?
May I have a moment, sir?
[MITAKA]
What is it? What?
[OFFICER C] How was the cream
puff? Feeling better now?
Yeah.
[OFFICER C] So, are you
ready to answer our questions?
The bossy one is Asahi,
and the quieter one is her
twin sister Yonaga.
[OFFICER C]
All right. And what's your name?
[OFFICERS gasp]
[MITAKA]
Uh...
[SANA]
The bossy one is Asahi,
and the quieter one is her
twin sister Yonaga.
[OFFICER C]
All right. And what's your name?
[OFFICERS gasp]
The bossy one is Asahi,
and the quieter one is her
twin sister Yonaga.
[OFFICER C]
All right. And what's your name?
Let's see it again,
but slower this time.
Yes, sir.
We must be missing something.
[OFFICER C]
It really happened.
She disappeared
right before my eyes.
And the footage
hasn't been altered in any way.
[MITAKA]
What about the twins?
A man came.
He told us he was
their guardian, so--
You let them go?!
Yes, we did.
[MITAKA]
They may have been children,
but you saw the
damage they caused!
I was just following
orders from above.
[MITAKA]
What?!
[POLICEMAN A]
We were told not to pursue
this case any further.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm?
You're free to go.
'Least for now.
You're being released due
to lack of evidence.
Your vehicle's out back.
You want me
to drive a wrecked car?
[ZOROKU]
Hmm?
Well, this is definitely my car.
How did it get repaired so fast?
This a free police service?
It wasn't us. We came
out and found it this way.
Then how did it get fixed?
Yeah, that's what
I want to know.
It's not just the car, the crash
scene was restored, too.
There's something going on here,
and I'd like to know what it is.
Going the wrong way
down a one-way street,
blowing through a red light,
speeding, and property damage.
With all you've done,
we should hold you overnight.
At least until
we got your story.
But there's no evidence.
Not even a scrap.
[GIRL STUDENT B] Where'd
they go? That's really weird.
[MITAKA]
We were thorough.
We checked all
the security cameras
in the area of the crash.
But there was nothing on them.
Reports were filed
by multiple sources.
And as you said before, there
were plenty of other witnesses.
We combed the scene again.
But we didn't even
find any skid marks.
[MAN A]
Why am I not getting any hits?
[MITAKA] Nothing at the parking
lot you said was destroyed.
No giant hole in the road.
Impossible.
[MITAKA]
You should be happy.
It means you've been exonerated.
Go home.
Forget about everything
that happened today. Got that?
[MITAKA]
Your fine's been dropped.
Have a nice afternoon.
[DRIVER A]
We've looked into the man
who was with the Red Queen.
And?
[DRIVER A]
His name is Zoroku Kashimura.
How would you
like us to proceed?
Keep him under surveillance?
I think not.
His involvement
seems to be incidental.
He simply got caught up in
events that were beyond him.
For the time being
at least, let's prioritize
recapturing the Red Queen.
[KITO]
Eat as much food as you'd like.
We can always order more.
[SUZUKI]
What? Are you serious?
[ZOROKU]
Sure am.
[SUZUKI]
All right.
Just give me a minute
to look it over, then.
We can get you a good
deal if that's what you want.
But are you sure
about getting rid of it?
Yeah.
[SUZUKI] From what I can tell,
the car seems to be
in good shape.
I don't get why
you'd want to ditch it.
[ZOROKU] Long story,
but some weird stuff happened.
Be careful with it.
[SUZUKI]
Okay.
[ZOROKU]
Hey, it's me.
I won't get into all of it,
but some stuff came up
that I had to deal with.
[ZOROKU] Sorry, but I need
you two to handle things
without me today.
Give me a call if you need to.
I'm just going to grab some food
and then head home.
[WAITER A]
Welcome!
I'll take a beer,
mutton stir-fry,
and fried bread on the side.
[WAITER A]
Got it.
[ZOROKU]
Can I use this ashtray?
[WAITER A]
Yeah, go ahead.
Here you go.
Great, thank you.
[SANA]
Do they have any cream puffs?
[ZOROKU grunts]
You pop up whenever
you feel like it, huh?
Where'd you come from this time?
That's a big drink.
Can I have some?
No, you can't.
It's not for kids.
Hey. Can I get an orange juice?
[WAITER A]
Sure. Comin' right up.
[ZOROKU]
Well? What do you want?
This part of the city is for
grown-ups, not lost little kids.
I don't need any
more trouble today.
[SANA]
Dreams of Alice.
Are we back to
the comic book thing again?
That's what the
people like me are called.
It's hard to explain,
but basically,
we've got
supernatural abilities.
[SANA] I don't know where
our powers came from
or why have them
and others don't.
--[ZOROKU gasps]
--[SANA] See this?
It's a vision called
a Mirror Gate.
We use these as intermediaries.
When we summon them, we have
to ability to materialize
any one thing we can imagine.
[SANA] Like a chain,
or a bow and arrows.
Some people can fix things, too.
And I suppose
this power of yours is how
you were able to drive my car?
[SANA]
That's right!
I'd never actually
driven before that,
but it wasn't very difficult
to get the hang of it.
[WAITER A]
Here ya go. One orange juice.
Mutton stir-fry with Chinese
onions, and fried bread.
[SANA whimpers]
--[ZOROKU] Are you done talking?
--Uh?
If so, then
leave and let me eat.
Don't want my food getting cold.
No! I'm not done, thank you!
I've officially
decided that I like you!
I'm gonna give you the honor
of becoming my servant,
Zoroku Kashimura!
You may show your gratitude now.
Ow, ow, ow!
Your feet belong
on the floor, not on the chair.
And when you're in a restaurant,
you will keep your voice
to a reasonable level.
[SANA]
Y-Yes, sir.
[SANA whines]
[ZOROKU]
Want some food?
Ah...
In the store,
you were staring at the meals.
When'd you last eat?
[SANA]
It's... been about three days.
I'm fine, though.
This long is nothing.
[sighs]
Hey! I've got another order.
[WAITER A]
What would you like?
[SANA whimpers]
Um... I can really eat this?
I don't have any
money to pay for it.
Yeah? It's a good thing I do.
[CUSTOMER A]
Wow, check that out!
[CUSTOMER B]
Is she training for
an eating competition
or something?
[SANA] I had no clue food was
so good in the outside world!
If you eat much
more you'll to explode.
[SANA] It's not something
I can control.
Activating the Mirror Gate takes
a tremendous amount of energy.
I need a lot of food to refuel.
Okay...
So that's why those girls were
eating when they attacked us.
Hold your chopsticks correctly!
[SANA] Chopsticks?
Is that what these are called?
You mean you don't
know how to use them?
[SANA sighs]
Gimme a break.
It's my first time outside
the research facility.
Earlier, you kept talking about
the two of us making a deal.
What is it that
you want from me?
[SANA sighs]
[WAITER A]
Thank you! Have a good night!
[SANA] What I want is to
crush the research facility.
That's the place you came from?
Yes, and there are many
other Dreams of Alice there,
with abilities like I have.
They're locked up,
and the things that happen
to them are terrible.
[SANA] I was able to escape,
but I can't do anything alone.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm...
I want you to help me.
When I looked inside
your mind before,
I saw that you're a good person.
[ZOROKU grunts]
I need your help to get
my friends away from there!
Please!
[WAITER A]
Hope you enjoyed everything!
[ZOROKU]
Let's go.
Uh?
[ZOROKU]
Well, are you coming?
It's so bright...
Come on, we don't
want to get separated.
You need to stick close to me.
How many times do I have
to tell you that this area isn't
a good place for kids
to be wandering around?
Uh... Coming!
[BARKER A]
Hey there, looking for company?
--We've got the prettiest...
--Is that guy talking to you?
And what kind of shop
is that, anyway?
It looks like a weird place.
[ZOROKU] Forget about it.
Just shut up and walk.
[SANA] Hey, wouldn't
it be easier to drive
wherever we're going?
[ZOROKU] The car creeped
me out, so I got rid of it.
[SANA]
Creeped you out? Why?
[ZOROKU] Would you
please just stop talking?
[ZOROKU] You ever
going to tell me your name?
[SANA groans]
You listening?
I asked you a question.
I thought you
told me to stop talking.
Now you can talk.
Your name?
[SANA]
Sana.
[ZOROKU]
What about your last name?
[SANA]
I don't know.
Huh...?
Truth is, I can't even
tell you where I came from.
I don't remember anything
before the facility.
And as for "Sana," Asahi
and Yonaga gave me that name.
Who are they,
some friends of yours?
The twin sisters
who were chasing us earlier.
Back at the facility,
they were the only ones
who called me that.
[YOUNG WOMAN A]
Yay! I got "very good luck."
[YOUNG MAN A]
I got "very bad luck."
Wow, I don't think I've
ever seen that one before.
Gee, thanks, that makes
me feel better.
[YOUNG WOMAN A]
It'll be okay.
I'll share half of my
"very good luck" with you.
[ZOROKU]
Only for a little while.
[SANA]
Huh?
[ZOROKU]
For a little while,
I'll give you food
and a place to stay.
But know this--
I don't give free rides,
so while you're with me,
you'll help with my work.
No work equals no food,
do you understand?
[SANA]
Okay! It's a deal!
I knew I'd get you
to come around!
If you wanna stay with me,
you better learn to be
respectful, you hear?!
[whines]
Don't expect me to baby you--
I promise that's
not gonna happen.
And one other thing.
I don't want you using
that weird power anymore.
[SANA]
Why not?!
I was serious about
granting you a wish.
But to do that,
I need to use my power.
[ZOROKU] Earlier, you said
you looked inside my mind.
Is that how you knew all
those things about me?
Uh, yeah? What's your point?
My name, birthdate,
my granddaughter.
You knew all that.
[SANA]
See? Amazing, right?
[sighs]
You're impossible.
You really don't
understand, do you?
[ZOROKU] You said you can do
anything you can imagine, right?
That's right.
And what if you used
that special power
of yours right here?
What, like now?
[ZOROKU]
You could do it, right?
Summon a big chain
or a wrecking ball?
You could cover
this whole place in blood.
[ZOROKU]
Get it now?
You mentioned a family member
I hadn't even spoke of,
and demanded that
I make a deal with you.
Then I found out you had this
potentially destructive power.
They've got a word
for that kind of thing--
it's blackmail.
[SANA] Wait, you've got it
wrong! I didn't mean to!
[ZOROKU] Whether you
meant to or not is irrelevant.
The threat in your words
remains the same.
I have no interest
in making a deal
or getting a wish granted.
It's more important to focus
on the people close to you,
than dream about things
that are out of reach.
You understand?
What you do is cheating,
and I hate crooked stuff.
[ZOROKU]
Listen.
That research facility,
whatever they do there--
Those are problems
for grown-ups.
What you should
focus on is changing
that twisted
temperament of yours.
If you want
to help your friends,
figure out how to
help yourself first.
What's wrong?
It's nothing...
[ZOROKU] You really don't know
how to talk to people, do you?
[cell phone vibrating]
[KITO]
Yes, it's me.
Understood.
I'll head that way
with the data now.
Shouldn't be long.
Yes. I'll see you soon.
Are we there yet...?
Not much longer.
Just hang in there.
[SANA groans]
'Kay...
[KITO] This is the Wonderland
the Red Queen created.
[t's located underneath
the research facility.
It's the children's playground,
a paradise brought to life
by randomly rewriting
the space's reality.
[BUSINESSMAN A]
You're saying she made this?
[BUSINESSMAN B]
That's unbelievable.
[KITO]
This is only the beginning.
Take a look at the next slide.
[BUSINESSMAN C]
What are those things?
[BUSINESSMAN D]
Are they alive?
As improbable
as it seems, they are.
They're amalgamations.
Created from images found in the
children's favorite storybooks.
There's still
much that's unclear.
The space inside
Wonderland is distorted.
It is now many thousands
of times its original size,
and it's still growing now.
[BUSINESSMAN D]
Is there anything about this
you do understand?
[KITO]
We are continuing to study it.
[BUSINESSMAN E] And?
How do you intend to proceed?
[KITO]
There are two problems.
Our first concern:
the person who possesses
this immense power is a
child who knows nothing
of the outside world.
If she remains unsupervised
in her current psychologically
unstable state, the existence
of the research facility
could possibly become
public knowledge.
The other problem is the
potential loss of the Red Queen
herself as a valuable
sample of this ability.
As such a loss would be
a massive detriment.
Not just to us,
but to the entire country.
[BUSINESSMAN A] And how do you
mean to address these problems?
Her capture will be conducted
with utmost discretion.
However, should something
happen that brings this incident
and the research facility itself
to the public's attention--
[BUSINESSMAN B]
What? Coercion?
[KITO]
Hmph.
[KITO] I would ask that you
recognize the situation
as a state of emergency
as soon as possible,
and recapture the Red Queen.
[ZOROKU]
Hey. Hey.
Come on. Get out.
[SANA]
Please tell me we're there.
[ZOROKU]
Not yet. This way. Follow me.
Here we are.
Where are we? Your house?
No. This is where I work.
Thanks to you,
I never made it in today.
I had to let the
young folks handle it.
[ZOROKU] But I at least
need to make sure things
are prepped for tomorrow.
Come in and wait for a bit.
Okay.
[SANA]
So, what do you do?
[gasps]
[SANA gasps]
[SANA]
All these flowers.
[ZOROKU]
Hmm? Well, what do you expect?
I'm a florist.
I didn't know that.
I specialize in arrangements
for events and gifts.
That sort of thing.
That's amazing.
They're really pretty.
[SAWAKI] So... this flower,
it's called, um...
Crap. Hold on.
I forgot.
What's it called again?
Come on, man.
Get it together.
What's the flower's name?
Damn it, I swear
I knew an hour ago.
Why the hell can't I remember?
Oh, yeah! Phlox! That's it!
It symbolizes...
[SAWAKI groans]
[MINIONS]
Have a good evening, sir.
[SAWAKI]
Yeah, sure.
What's up?
He's all dressed up, and
he seems kinda nervous.
The boss has got
big plans tonight.
[SAWAKI'S MINION F]
Cutting off someone's finger?!
[SAWAKI'S MINION G]
No, you idiot!
He's seeing his girlfriend.
He's going to propose to her.
That's why he's got the
flower arrangement done
special by Kashimura.
[SAWAKI'S MINION F] Th-That
old guy from this afternoon?
He really was a florist?
I know it's late,
I won't be much longer.
So tired... Where are we going?
[ZOROKU]
Home, this time.
[SANA] Don't tell me
we have to walk there, too...
[ZOROKU] You're not
the one doing the walking.
[SANA sighs]
[ZOROKU]
You're not sleeping there.
Come upstairs.
[SANA groans]
[ZOROKU]
Take off your shoes.
[ZOROKU] I'm not using this
room for anything right now.
It's a little bit dusty,
but I think you'll survive.
Here's some fresh bedding.
I'll get you a clean
change of clothes.
'Kay... Thank you...
They're my granddaughter's,
so they'll be
pretty big, but you--
[ZOROKU]
Hmm...
Zoroku... Cream puffs...
[SANA]
"Dreams of Alice."