[ZOROKU]
Thanks for coming.
Sorry for calling
you in so late.
Nah, don't worry about it, Boss.
We don't mind.
So, what's up?
Is something wrong?
Actually, there are a few
things I wanted to tell you.
[ICHIJO]
Wow, you brought a lot of stuff.
I did.
I figured Sana would
probably be hungry,
so I wanted to make sure we had
plenty of her favorite snacks.
That's good thinking.
[ZOROKU] I've already let our
clients know that I'll be away
for a bit, but I'll need the
two of you to keep an eye
on the shop while I'm gone,
if you think you're up for it.
[CHINATSU]
Yeah, totally.
[ICHIRO]
We've got it covered.
Thank you.
[BOTH gasp]
[SANAE]
He's heading back.
[BOTH]
All right!
[HATORI]
No good. There's no service.
[SANA]
"No service"?
Like, when you go
through a tunnel?
[HATORI]
Yeah.
It's never actually happened
with my phone before.
[SANA]
We're probably really far down.
I think we're in the deepest
part of Wonderland.
[HATORI]
It happened so fast,
but we fell from
up there, right?
I think so.
Okay. Then all we have
to do is find a way up
and get back to that door.
[SANA]
I don't know.
I don't believe you!
You have to know!
You're just saying that to be
mean to me, aren't you?
No, I'm just as
confused as you are!
I don't know what's going on,
but I can't use my
power like normal.
And I've never been to
this part of Wonderland,
so I don't know my way around.
[gasps] Where are you going?
[HATORI]
Where do you think?
To look for a way out.
I'm not really sure
that's a good idea.
Hey! You don't
know how far it is.
You could get tired!
Uh! Hold on, I'm coming!
[gasps, yelps]
[SANA]
Hey!
Wait for me.
[ZOROKU] I thought they
deserved to know everything.
[SANAE]
Huh?
I told them about
where Sana came from.
About her power,
and what she can do with it.
It seemed only fair.
Sorry.
I know Naito told us to keep
this as quiet as possible.
Well, given the situation,
you didn't have much choice.
I'm guessing they were
pretty surprised about it all?
[ZOROKU]
Nah, they already knew
something was
different about her.
[ICHIJO]
So, what did they say?
[ZOROKU chuckles]
Hardly anything.
"Well, Sana's still Sana,
right?" That was it.
[ICHIJO] Ah. I'm sure Sana
would be happy to hear that.
[SANA groaning]
Uh?
[SANA sighs]
Hey! It's never gonna work!
[ICHIJO] Despite the fact that
Sana was born in Wonderland,
we still don't know
very much about it.
I want you both to be careful
while we're in there.
Oh.
I thought the name made it
sound like an amusement park.
Huh?
Are you worried?
[ZOROKU]
Hm? Why? Are you?
[SANAE]
Mm...
I was really scared when
those people took Sana before.
I hated thinking that she
might never come back.
But in the end, it all
worked out, didn't it?
So, I've officially decided it
will be okay this time, too.
You think so?
[SANAE]
Of course!
I'm the alien of happy
endings, so it has to be!
[gasps] Naito was the one
driving last time.
I hope that doesn't matter.
[ICHIJO] Are you saying you'd
rather have Naito here instead?
[SANAE]
No, I think you'll do just fine.
[ICHIJO]
That's a relief.
[SANA grunting]
[HATORI laughs]
I'm back!
[HATORI]
Nothing...
[SANA]
I told you, it wouldn't work.
I think when my power
disappeared, the exit did, too.
I'm pretty sure we're stuck.
We can't be stuck!
I have to get back home to my
mom, she needs me with her.
Send me home right now!
I... I want to go home, too!
I'm not lying!
[SANA] Hey, I don't
think anyone's there.
Are you ever gonna
believe anything I say?
[whines]
[NORIKO] Our theory is
that the person with Sana is
the girl responsible for
the Harajuku incident.
There's no cell signal
where they are,
so we can't get
any specific intel.
The thing is,
Wonderland is in a
constant state of flux.
But aside from confirming
both girls are in there,
we're shut out now.
We haven't been able learn
anything that's going on inside.
There's no telling what kind of
dangers you might encounter.
Please keep your
guards up at all times.
[LAB MAN A]
We still can't see it?
[LAB MAN B]
We can verify there's a signal,
but that's all.
[LAB MAN C] The energy
coming from inside is stronger.
[LAB MAN A]
Does that mean it's expanding?
[LAB MAN B]
Most likely, yes.
[LAB MAN A]
Will it affect this world?
[LAB MAN C]
Calculating that now.
[SECURITY SYSTEM]
To access,
please enter your
12-digit passcode.
[SANAE]
This is it?
This is the place
where Sana was born?
The girls are lost
in here somewhere,
and we need to find them.
Yes.
Ahh! So cute!
[ICHIJO grunts]
[NORIKO groaning]
I just can't help myself.
I love it when you
change forms like that!
Yamada, remind me
what your job is here?
Provide backup if you need it,
and collect as much data on
Wonderland as possible.
Not to be a one-woman fan club.
[SANAE]
Grandpa, what are you doing?
[ICHIJO]
Kashimura, please wait.
[HATORI]
Excuse me! Is anybody in here?
If so, please say something!
[HATORI]
Is anyone home? Hello?
[SANA panting]
What is it?
Did you see something?
[SANAE]
Hey, that's Sana!
It looks like the night the
twins stayed over at our house.
Cool statue.
[ZOROKU]
Hm?
[SANAE gasps]
What do ya know.
That's the stuffed pig
I bought her, only... bigger.
[PIG oinking]
[ICHIJO, SANAE]
Uh?
[SANAE]
Hey! That's the real one!
That's what we have to do!
If we follow that pig,
it will lead us to Sana!
No offense, but isn't
that kind of random?
No, I don't think it is.
I don't have any better ideas.
[gasps]
Right, let's go!
[ICHIJO] Maybe we should
think this through.
Kashimura?
Kashimura!
[ZOROKU] Is this this something
from another of Sana's memories?
I can't really tell.
I'll take a look at
it from up above.
Number 41.
[gasps]
[yelps]
[SANAE]
Ichijo!
Mommy...
[SANA]
I'm sorry.
[HATORI grunting]
I was only trying to get
you back for what happened.
I had no idea we'd end up
stuck in Wonderland.
It's my fault.
I got us into this whole mess.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
I'm partially to blame, too.
[SANAE]
Ichijo just disappeared.
Do you think she's
going to be okay?
[ZOROKU] Maybe we should ask
the alien of happy endings.
[SANAE gasps]
What would she have to say?
[SANAE] She'd say that
Ichijo is really strong.
[ZOROKU]
Yeah. She'll be fine.
[whistling]
[BOTH gasp]
--[ZOROKU groans]
--[SANAE screams]
What was that?
It's starting to feel like
somebody is mocking us.
When we're all finished here,
I'm gonna have to give
this Wonderland place
a good talking to.
Totally!
Wonderland could definitely
use a Grandpa lecture!
[HATORI]
Hey, what's going on out there?
[SANA] I could be wrong,
but I think it's practicing.
I don't understand.
What is it practicing?
[SANA]
Things it's learned.
[HATORI]
I still don't get it.
[SANA]
Wonderland is always curious.
It wants to know what
the world is made of.
You know, things
like colors, shapes,
smells, and flavors.
But it's more than that, too.
I think it wants to
know about the rules
that control the world.
It wants to understand
what makes plants grow
and why the sun shines.
How humans see the world, and
why they do the things they do.
What life is--
where it comes from.
Why it exists.
I think it gathers
things from our world
and imitates them here,
trying to understand.
I wonder if that's what
the Mirror Gates are.
If they're like peepholes
Wonderland uses.
A way for it to
spy on our world.
It wasn't always
like this, you know.
In the beginning, Wonderland
was only a little bigger
than the room
we're in right now.
Eventually, I think it will
be a whole universe.
[HATORI]
It's strange.
Uh?
I'm listening to you talk,
and everything you're
saying is so out there,
it's impossible to believe.
But for some reason,
I think I believe it all anyway.
You're a mysterious girl,
you know that?
I'm not some weirdo!
I didn't call you a weirdo.
[SANA]
I'm not lying!
I didn't say you were
lying, either.
You're so funny.
[SANA]
I am not funny!
You know,
it would be nice to be able
to transform yourself
whenever you want,
like this place does.
Uh...?
[HATORI]
This world is very strange.
And I can't pretend
to understand it.
But it's beautiful.
[HATORI] If you're right--
if Wonderland is eventually
going to become
its own universe,
maybe I could just
live here forever
instead of going back home.
[HATORI]
I didn't mean to,
but it looks like I've
run away, after all.
[SANA]
I don't know.
Are you sure about that?
Sure about what?
[SANA]
Uh, I-I just mean...
If you stay here forever,
you'll probably get bored.
And didn't you say you needed
to go back home to your mom?
[HATORI]
Leave me alone.
You wouldn't understand.
Uh.
[HATORI]
Sorry.
[gasps]
I shouldn't have said that.
It was mean.
This is difficult.
I'm not sure where to start.
[SANA]
Uh...
My mom hates me.
That's what it comes down to.
The word "mom" is a shorter
version of "mother," right?
[HATORI]
Yeah, that's right.
I thought so.
My Sanae also had a mother.
Her mother's father is Zoroku,
her grandpa.
I never had a mother or father,
so I don't really get it.
You don't have parents?
[SANA]
Nope.
[HATORI]
Hey. Can I tell you something?
[SANA]
Sure.
My parents are unhappy.
It's hard to remember
a time when they weren't
always fighting
with each other.
Why do they fight?
Because I failed my elementary
school entrance exam.
My mom was
so disappointed in me.
[SANA]
Hm?
I'm such a pathetic
excuse for a daughter,
she can't even look
me in the eye anymore.
That's why it's probably better
for me not to be there.
If I'm gone, then Mom and
Dad won't have anything
to fight about, and they
can go back to being happy.
Things are really bad now.
But it wasn't always like this.
Lately, it's like my mom
is a different person,
looking out at the world from
a dark universe of her own.
When she looks
at me like that,
it breaks my heart.
I love my mother,
and I always will.
But I hate seeing her in pain
and knowing that
it's because of me...
That she would
probably be happy
if only she didn't have
me for a daughter.
[cries]
[HATORI]
I... don't want to go home.
I'm useless.
I should never have existed!
[HATORI sobs]
[SANA]
Hey. I'm sorry.
You might not like
hearing this from me, but...
For what it's worth,
I think it's okay
that you exist.
[gasps]
Thanks for saying that.
[SANA]
Not just you.
I think there's nobody
who should exist,
and nobody who
shouldn't, either.
Because if that were true,
then I wouldn't be here.
It scares me to think about
these kinds of things.
It makes me feel so... small.
You wanna know
a secret about me?
I was actually born here.
Huh?
[SANA] I know I look like
a human, but I'm not one.
In fact, I think
I'm Wonderland itself.
[whistle blows]
[COACH A]
We're done for the day.
[STUDENTS]
Thanks, Coach!
Wanna grab some food?
[BOY STUDENT A]
Ice cream!
[BOY STUDENT C]
Sure.
[PHONE RECORDING]
The number you have dialed
is out of the service area.
Please hang up and try
your call at another time.
[AYUMU]
Where are you?
[HATORI]
You're not human?
[SANA]
Mm-mm.
Huh? Wha...?
Hey, wait.
Uh, what are you doing?
Um... Honestly,
I was told never to
tell anyone this stuff,
but it feels kinda
good to talk about it.
When I was born here,
I was something else.
Something I can't explain,
and don't really understand.
I didn't look like this then.
I wasn't even shaped
like a human at that point.
Then, before I knew it,
everything changed.
Suddenly, I had eyes and hands--
a normal-looking human body.
It's hard to remember it all,
but I'm pretty sure I was
part of Wonderland.
You don't believe me, huh?
No. I'm just surprised.
I figured it out after
I saw you that day.
You and I were similar, and it
made me feel all frazzled.
I've thought about it,
and I'm pretty sure I'm still
connected to this place somehow.
The outside world and
real humans are what Wonderland
wants to know about.
So, I'm just like some sort
of communication device.
A way for it to get the
answers it's looking for.
Except, if that's true,
then there are plenty of others
who could take my place.
And that would mean
I don't actually matter.
There's no good reason
for me to even exist.
[HATORI gasps]
[SANA] I guess what I'm saying
is that I kinda know how
you feel, because
sometimes I wonder
if I'm really
supposed to be here.
If I deserve to have
anyone care about me.
[cries]
Oh, um... I'm sorry,
did I say something wrong?
I don't have a mom,
so I probably shouldn't
compare myself to you.
Okay, well, maybe I
could wipe your tears?
[HATORI]
No.
You know, life's different
since I left Wonderland.
I've found lots of new things
that make me happy.
I've met so many people,
tasted yummy food,
played fun games.
Had exciting adventures.
Of course, there's been
annoying stuff, too--
things that make
me feel frazzled.
And at first, I thought
that stuff was wrong.
I mean, if it made me feel bad,
how could I need it in my life?
I'd be better off
without it, right?
But now, I don't
think that's true.
That stuff--the things
that frazzle me--
I need them as much as I need
the things that make me happy.
What I mean is,
you said it'd be better
if you weren't around,
but I think you're
wrong about that.
Yeah, sure, you frazzle me,
a whole bunch--
[HATORI laughs]
Uh?
[HATORI]
I was right.
You really are
a mysterious girl.
It's kinda cool.
You really think I'm mysterious?
Stop that. What are you doing?
My Sanae does this to me when
I'm upset about something.
"Your Sanae"?
[SANA]
Yeah.
All the people I know are big.
They treat me like a little kid.
When I talk about
stuff like this,
I feel like they're not
really listening.
I try to tell them how
frustrated and confused I am,
but they just say
I'm doing great
or I'll understand
when I'm older.
[laughs]
[gasps]
So, how old are you, then?
[SANA]
Uh, I don't know.
Between eight and ten?
Well.
That means we're probably
around the same age.
[SANA] Maybe, but I'm pretty
sure I'm older than you are.
I don't think so.
I'm totally older than you.
No, I'm older!
[SANA gasps]
[HATORI] Can I stay
like this for a little bit?
[HATORI] When I was little,
my mom held me like this a lot.
[HATORI] I walked in
and introduced myself,
but all the other kids
started laughing at me
and saying I was weird.
When the teacher told me I
didn't have to introduce myself
when I entered
the classroom,
they all just laughed
at me again.
[HATORI'S MOM] Don't worry
about the other kids, dear.
You did fine.
You introduced yourself
just like I told you to,
and I'm very proud.
[HATORI'S MOM]
It'll be all right, little one.
Mommy's got you. You're okay.
[HATORI]
Do you remember that day, Mom?
I was so sad, but at the same
time, I was happy, too.
You made me feel safe.
I felt lucky to have
a mom like you.
It's just like back then.
[HATORI]
I can hear her heart beating.
So, listen.
I've decided I do want
to see my mom again.
Will you help me?
Yeah!
[HATORI]
Thank you.
[SANA]
"I'm Home."