[SOSUKE grunts]
[footsteps]
Sosuke, what are you doing?
If you don't hurry,
you'll miss Rin's race!
What's that? Hey,
is everything okay?
[SOSUKE]
Don't worry about it. I'm fine.
Sure, whatever you say.
[IWATOBI CLUB] Last lap,
last lap, last lap, last lap!
[IWATOBI CLUB]
All right, Rei!
Man, that was his best time yet.
[AMAKATA] But it's not enough
to get him to the finals.
[GOU] Nagisa's breaststroke
time wasn't enough
to make the cut, either.
[AMAKATA]
It's hard to break past the wall
to get to Nationals, isn't it?
[ANNOUNCER 10A]
Men's one-hundred meter.
Butterfly. Group three.
[NITORI, MOMOTARO]
Go, Rin!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
[REFEREE 10A]
Ready...
[beep]
[CROWD] Go!
[MINAMI]
Ready! Fight!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB] Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
[gasping]
[MAKOTO]
Huh?
Haru...
[SOSUKE sighs]
[YOUNG SOSUKE gasps]
I'm not happy about losing,
but you know what?
That was a pretty good
showing for our first relay.
Our take away from this
should be that we can all--
[YOUNG SOSUKE]
I've had enough.
Relay team's just not for me.
I don't wanna lose
'cause of someone else.
Or even worse, for you guys
to lose because of me.
It's not my thing, man.
Tch!
Who do you think you are?
Take it back. Now!
[REFEREES] --That's enough!
--What is going on with you two?
[YOUNG KISUMI] You talked
smack about the relay.
Of course he got mad.
Rin's Dad swam the relay in
school, too, it's pretty much
the most important
thing in his life.
Yeah, I know how
much he loves it.
But you'd think
I told him his father
was a moron or something.
If you don't wanna
swim it for yourself,
you should swim it for him.
It's a nice thought, but no.
[YOUNG KISUMI gasps]
We don't do things
for each other.
That's just not how we are.
[YOUNG KISUMI]
Oh. Well,
guess that's what
it is to be rivals.
You're right on the money.
We are rivals. We always
push each other.
[YOUNG SOSUKE]
Hey, Rin.
[YOUNG RIN]
What?
[YOUNG SOSUKE] Do you
wanna do a butterfly race?
No thanks.
Right.
I'll only race
hundred-meter freestyle.
You're on, man!
The loser has bathroom duty
for an entire week!
Hope you like cleaning, then!
[YOUNG RIN] Their relay
team's got a real solid rep.
It's callin' my name.
[YOUNG SOSUKE gasps]
[RIN]
Sosuke. What's wrong?
[SOSUKE gasps]
Did something happen?
Nitori was worried about you.
[SOSUKE]
Everything's fine.
[RIN] You were weird this
morning when we practiced
in the sub pool, too.
You just up and took off.
[SOSUKE] Don't worry
about it, it's nothing.
[RIN] Look man, when you
miss practice like that,
I'm gonna worry.
You wanna tell me
where you were?
Come on, dude. You gotta
talk to me here--
I just said it was nothing!
[RIN sighs]
[RIN]
Sosuke.
Incoming.
[SOSUKE]
Huh?
[SOSUKE grunts]
Your shoulder's in pretty
bad shape, isn't it?
[RIN]
Let me see it.
[SOSUKE]
Piss off!
[RIN, SOUSUKE grunt]
[RIN gasps]
[RIN]
When did this happen?
[SOSUKE]
This morning.
It's really not
as bad as it looks.
[RIN]
Oh, come on!
You and I both know it
didn't happen this morning!
[SOSUKE sighs]
Well I guess I can't slip
anything by you, can I?
The truth is, I injured it
about two years ago.
I pushed myself
too hard in training.
But you were
already being scouted.
Why push it when you knew
what college you were going to?
[SOSUKE]
'Cause I didn't. I lied.
No one scouted me.
[RIN gasps]
[GIRL 10A] You wanna go
watch the next race?
[GIRL 10B]
Yeah!
[SOSUKE sighs]
Can we get out of here?
[CROWD cheers]
Man, I wasn't even close.
Neither was I.
But I guess that's
Regionals for ya.
Well, this competition
isn't over yet!
Right. Well put.
The relay will be our
chance to shine.
Great work back there, you guys.
Seriously? Thanks.
Hey. Why you all by
yourself? Where's Haru?
I don't know, He took off
after his argument with Rin.
I tried looking for him,
but he hasn't turned up yet.
No big deal.
He'll come back, he's just
waitin' for the race to start.
Of course.
You heard how solemn he
sounded in the locker room.
[HARUKA]
Listen. It's okay. We're a team.
I'm gonna swim relay.
I didn't come this far not to.
I know he cares as much
about this as we do!
I trust him implicitly.
He'll be here.
He will. You're right.
[RIN]
You have something here!
If you'd just take it seriously
for once in your life!
[RIN]
Answer me, Sosuke!
[NITORI] Hey, Rin!
Are you guys here, or..?
Um...
Dude, what's up?
Did you see the
individual medley?
Everyone was super fired up!
Awesome.
Momo, stop!
When's the last time
you saw Rin and Sosuke?
Huh?
[RIN]
Tell me why.
Why did you lie to me?
I think I have a right to know.
You and me are like rivals.
We shouldn't be
on the same team.
At least that's how
I used to see it.
When you told me you were
transferring to Iwatobi,
I didn't say a word.
Why would I?
And when I started
middle school,
all I did was focus on swimming.
You were off chasing
your dreams in Australia.
So I figured I would
work toward my own dream.
After a while, your
letters stopped coming.
I kept rooting for you, though.
I knew you'd break through
that wall one way or another.
Once I got into high school,
I got even more obsessed
with my training.
My dream was gonna happen,
no matter what the cost.
I used to imagine what
it'd be like when I'd
finally made it to a
big International meet.
Every time I pictured it,
you were right there beside me.
Those were crazy times.
I trained hard,
all day, every day.
No one could touch me.
I was the best.
And that's when it happened.
My shoulder starting
giving me issues.
Nothing I couldn't
handle, at first.
So I ignored it
and kept on going.
Eventually, it got worse.
Every day it hurt
a little more.
But no matter how bad it got,
I refused to give up.
I had to get stronger. It's
like my dream was out there,
calling from a distance,
mocking me.
I stayed at it,
but before long,
my shoulder finally gave out.
It was the summer
of my freshman year.
You wanna know why I lied?
'Cause when Gou told
me you were back.
I didn't want you
to see me that way.
to know the truth.
I just couldn't handle it,
for you of all people
to see me all broken down.
Rehab. Injury. Rehab.
That was my routine.
Day in, day out.
A busted rotator cuff makes
it hard to come in first.
I got sick of being a loser.
Truth is, I was miserable.
And then one day,
I accepted reality.
No matter what I did,
my dream wasn't gonna happen.
So I turned my back
on swimming for good.
[RIN gasps]
[HARUKA gasps]
[RIN]
You quit swimming?
But I wanted to see you
compete one last time
before I decided to retire.
So I dropped in on
last year's Regionals.
Wait, you actually
saw that race?
Yeah.
I wanted to watch the best
swimmer I've ever known
accomplish a goal
we used to share.
Thing is, when I saw you
struggling the way you were,
what can I say?
It broke my heart.
I thought you were the type
of guy who could overcome
any obstacle,
burst through any wall.
But something was wrong.
Something must've happened.
[RIN]
I give up. I quit years ago
and I should've stayed quit!
[SOSUKE]
I wanted to call out to you...
But the words wouldn't come.
And then, in the relay
you swam with Haruka,
you went at it
with such intensity,
it's like you were
a changed man.
Seeing you with
the guys afterwards,
the way you were laughing
and carryin' on...
I dunno.
It gave me a little twinge
of hope, I suppose.
The old dream came back to life.
You and me were gonna
swim side by side.
Honestly,
I didn't know what
it meant to you.
How important it was
to swim as part of a team.
I realize It's over for me.
But, before I go...
I wanna swim the
best darn relay I can!
With you. Today.
[RIN gasps]
[RIN] Idiot! Why didn't
you tell me sooner?
Why did you lie to me? Why?
Because if you'd have known,
it would've broken your heart.
[RIN sniffles]
You son of a-- you just--
[SOSUKE]
Come on.
The race is about to start.
Are you nuts?
You can't swim a relay in
the condition you're in!
[SOSUKE]
Oh, yes I can.
Dude, if you push
yourself too hard,
you really will be done!
I know.
That was the idea
from the start.
Forget it! I won't let
you hurt yourself!
I'm doing this whether
you want me to or not,
that's all there is to it.
Make your peace with that.
Yeah right!
[SOSUKE]
I'll make you a promise.
I'll see this race
through to the end.
'Cause that's my dream.
What's left of it anyway.
No!
[NITORI]
Let him swim!
It's the right thing to do!
[MOMOTARO]
Yeah, come on.
[RIN]
You guys? How did you--?
We are a team!
I've wanted to swim with you
ever since I saw you
compete at Regionals.
That's how long I've
waited for this honor.
Please, don't take
that away from me!
Sosuke put a lot of
time into my training.
Let me show you what I've got!
[MOMOTARO]
That's right! Come on, man!
How many people get to say
they were part of something
larger than themselves?
Isn't that what
this is all about?
Who cares if it's all
off the table tomorrow?
We can give it all
we've got today!
[NITORI]
We're your dream team!
[MOMOTARO]
Heck yeah we are!
[SOSUKE]
You know they're right.
And you're our captain.
Let's do this while we can.
[RIN gasps]
[MAKOTO]
Ah! Haru!
[REI]
There you are!
Sorry if I made you worry.
We knew you'd be here!
[MAKOTO] They're gonna
be calling us soon.
Let's go.
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
[ANNOUNCER 10A]
Ladies and gentlemen.
Next up on the docket
we have the men's
one-hundred meter
medley relay finals.
[REI]
Look at his shoulder.
I think he's hurt.
I wonder what happened to him.
That looks excruciating.
Do you think he's planning
on swimming with that?
[HARUKA] There's something
you should know.
I heard Sosuke saw me and
Rin run the relay last year.
[NAGISA, REI, MAKOTO]
Huh?
Watching us overcome
the odds and win,
Sosuke found his dream.
He realized how special it is
to be able to swim with friends.
And even though his shoulder was
screwed up, he was determined
to fight through the pain
and give it another go.
Even if it costs
him his future.
You guys.
All I want is for you to go
out there and do your best!
[REI, NAGISA, MAKOTO]
Yeah!
If I were you,
I wouldn't let my
guard down out there.
Good advice.
If I were you, I'd probably
tell myself the same thing.
You're 'bout to see
my backstroke, dude!
Can you handle that?
Heh. Don't know, thing is,
I'll be too busy
swimming to notice.
I intend to win.
What a coincidence.
That's exactly what we
had in mind for ourselves.
I just want you to
know this is our team.
Our best team.
Yeah?
Well, the same thing
goes for us, man.
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 10A]
Ready. Set.
[beep]
[CROWD]
Go!
Momo's so fast!
Right off the platform!
He's already got
a lead on Iwatobi!
[GOU]
Wait!
Makoto's speed is in
his stroke not his start!
The longer he stays at it,
the faster he goes!
[AMAKATA] Look, he's
catching up with Samezuka!
[RIN, SOUSUKE]
Momo!
--[HARUKA] Makoto!
--[REI] Come on!
[UOZUMI]
It's close!
They tied!
[MAKOTO]
Nagisa!
His relay exchange was perfect!
Guess their practice paid off!
[HANAMURA]
Wow!
Look how quickly
they took the lead!
--[MAKOTO] Come on, buddy!
--[REI] Nagisa!
[RIN]
Come on! Swim!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Oh no...
His shoulder looks hurt.
[AMAKATA]
They're still tied!
[NAGISA]
Swim, Rei!
[NITORI]
Go!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB murmuring]
[MIKOSHIBA]
What's this all about?
I don't know what the heck
you guys think you're doing
right now, but I know
what you should be doing,
and that's cheering
your teammates on!
[UOZUMI]
Ready! Fight!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB] Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
[GOU] Oh no, Sosuke's
catching up to Rei!
[AMAKATA]
He's widening his lead!
[SOSUKE grunts]
[SOSUKE yelps]
[MOMOTARO, NITORI]
Swim, Sosuke!
Sosuke!
[SOSUKE gasps]
[SOUSUKE yells]
All right!
Last spurt!
Rin!
[MAKOTO] It looks like
they're both speeding up!
Those guys are amazing!
They entered the turn
at the exact same time!
--[MAKOTO] Haru! Swim!
--[REI] Come on, Haru!
[NAGISA]
Do it, Haru!
--[MOMOTARO] Swim! Rin!
--[SOSUKE] Go!
[HARUKA, RIN yell]
[NAGISA, REI, MAKOTO]
Yeah! We did it!
[CROWD cheering]
Oh wow! They're going
to Nationals!
[GOU, HANAMURA gasp, giggle]
[HARUKA panting]
[MAKOTO]
Haru!
We did it,
can you believe it?
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
This is so amazing,
we made Nationals!
I can't even begin
to process this!
Good job, guys.
I'm proud of all of us.
[MOMOTARO yells]
That rocked!
Yeah!
Yeah. It sure did!
[MOMOTARO, RIN, NITORI laugh]
Thanks you guys.
Huh?
Look at Sosuke bein'
a big cheese ball.
[RIN, NITORI laugh]
[SOSUKE]
Rin.
Well...
I think I finally found
what I was looking for.
[RIN gasps]
[RIN]
Took you long enough.
[SOSUKE laughs]
[HARUKA] The sky never changes.
Neither does the ocean.
Sometimes it feels
like nothing changes.
[MAKOTO]
What are you talking about?
They're always changing.
That's their nature.
Like us. Like everyone.
[HARUKA] Next time:
"Backstroke Turn of Fate."
[MAKOTO]
Haru.
You know what?