Holy...
This is insane!
[NITORI gasps]
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Whoa!
[SAMEZUKA 9A]
He broke Iwashimizu's record!
All right! Way to
kill it, Nitori!
Looks like someone's
coaching bumped our boy's
game up a notch.
Shut up, man.
[MOMOTARO]
You are now officially my idol!
I'm totally serious!
There's no way you're not going
to Regionals with that time!
[NITORI] Whoa there champ,
you're gonna jinx me.
Nothing's written in stone yet.
Whatever! Dude, you gotta
let me in on your routine!
It's like some kind of
super ultra-secret, huh?
Sosuke just gave me a few
pointers on the side,
that's all there was to it.
Aww no fair, man!
I want some pointers!
Ugh. Just great.
[MOMOTARO]
C'mon! Please!
[RIN]
Ai.
Don't let today go to your head,
Regionals are still up in
the air. No gettin' comfortable.
[NITORI laughs]
Yes, sir!
[AMAKATA]
You're still practicing?
My goodness, it's so late.
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, but--
[AMAKATA] It's way past closing
time, the guidance counselor
is going to blow a gasket
if he sees you boys here
at this hour.
We're comin' up on the
last week before Regionals.
We gotta squeeze in
all the practice we can.
Our times are good, but the
exchanges need tweaking
if we expect to have a shot.
Whaddya say we
give it another go?
Sure.
[AMAKATA]
Exchanges?
[MAKOTO]
Right.
Those milliseconds between
one guy touching the platform
and the next one diving in.
Tightening up that trade-off
moment is what separates
the men from the boys.
[MAKOTO] The idea is to predict
your partner's end time.
If you can anticipate the moment
he's gonna touch the platform
without having to watch him,
you can tweak your dive stance
to get the most
out of your entry.
We're trying to shave our
exchange times down to zero.
[AMAKATA] Isn't that
cutting if awfully close?
I mean, what happens
if you hit the water
before the other's
reached the wall?
[NAGISA]
Instant disqualification.
It's just one of the
risks you learn to accept
for the sake of the team.
Miss A, we know it's late,
but mastering this technique
is gonna give us an edge
against the competition.
[PRINCIPAL 9A]
Practice is running long, I see.
[MAKOTO]
Oh. Hello, sir.
[AMAKATA]
Oh no, it's the principal!
I'm dreadfully sorry, sir!
I just told these boys it's
well past time to wrap up!
[COUNSELOR 9A]
Ah, you're fine. No harm done.
[PRINCIPAL 9A]
Stay as long as you need.
It's not often one our own
gets scouted by the pros.
Eh, Nanase?
We haven't been this excited
about Regionals
in quite some time.
Every member of the faculty
is as thrilled as can be.
Do your school proud.
[HARUKA]
Yes, sir.
[GOU]
Oh, by the way.
I thought you might get a kick
out of knowing that Nitori's
on the short list for
Samezuka's Regionals team.
[NAGISA]
I get to swim against Aye-Aye?
This'll be a piece of cake!
Though, I suppose
any way you slice it,
we'll have our work cut out
for us with So-So and Rin.
[REI]
Who on earth is "So-so?"
Oh. That's great news!
Then Sosuke's shoulder
must be healed!
[NAGISA]
That's my nickname for Sosuke.
[GOU]
Hey, Makoto, something wrong?
Huh? I'm good.
I was just wondering
if you'd heard about
anything going on with Yamazaki?
[GOU]
Like what?
Uh-- Actually, forget it,
I don't even know.
[MAKOTO] You think what
Kisumi told us is for real?
I don't know, man.
Could be gossip.
I mean, the guy
is still swimming.
I guess you got a point.
Either way it doesn't
really matter,
what we need to worry about
right now is ourselves.
[NAGISA]
This place is huge!
Wow. Quite an upgrade from
where we stayed last year.
[MAKOTO] Watch us get stuck
in a broom closet while Miss A
and Gou get a tricked out
presidential suite
or something.
[REI] I do not need a flashback
to training camp right now.
Please, it's not the same thing.
That's right.
You gentlemen are
the stars of this show,
so you get star treatment.
Before you go nuts,
remember the old proverb:
"Nothing in this world
is more expensive
than that which comes free,
for it is invaluable!"
Or something like that.
The main take-away is no
belly-aching about the rooms.
[BOYS]
Yes, ma'am.
[MOMOTARO]
Hey!
Gou!
[GOU]
Oh look, it's Rin!
Well! What do ya know?
I guess we're all stayin'
at the same hotel.
[NAGISA] Waddup, Aye-Aye!
How's it goin'?
[NITORI] How many times
do I have to ask you
not to call me that?
Oh, Sosuke, I've been meaning
to ask why you were all
cloak-and-dagger
at the station
near our house the
other day? Kinda weird.
Uh. What?
Yo! I'm pouring
my heart out to you
and you pass me up to give
Sosuke the third degree?
The Otter needs some
tender love and care!
Fact: My fav ice cream bar
is chocolate pudding!
Fact: When ordering a hamburger,
I always go for triple cheese!
Fact: The sorta gal guaranteed
to drive me crazy--
[RIN]
Is off limits!
[SOSUKE]
I should go.
[GOU]
Uh. Yeah, sure.
[RIN] Everybody get
settled into their rooms
and meet back here
in twenty. Understood?
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Yes, sir!
[GOU]
Okay, fellahs! It's chow time!
Miss Amakata gave us enough
cash to feed a small army,
so pick whatever looks good!
Does it have to be healthy?
[HARUKA]
This is my pick.
[NAGISA]
Cool!
Naturally.
Of course.
[MIKOSHIBA laughing]
That's a pretty good one,
[GOU]
Is that who I think it is?
[REI]
What's he doing here?
[MIKOSHIBA]
Hey!
Gou, sweetheart, we gotta
stop meetin' like this.
[NAGISA, REI, GOU]
Hey, Mikoshiba.
[MAKOTO]
And who might this be?
Ah! Lemme introduce
you to Todou,
my university's top scout!
Seriously?
[MIKOSHIBA]
I figured I'd show him
what the Samezuka
team's capable of.
Is that by chance
Nanase from Iwatobi?
You bet!
Wait a second, this man's
actually heard of Haru?
[TODOU]
In my line of work, who hasn't?
Hi there. Honor to
meet you, young man.
You've got quite the reputation.
After that District
tournament, your freestyle
has become something
of a minor legend.
You've been on my
radar for a while.
Mine and every college
with a swim team.
Not to sound preachy,
but are you even aware
how much potential
you have, son?
Can't let that
talent go to waste.
Stay focused and the sky's
the limit, I assure you.
You'll have lots of eyes
on you in tomorrow's race.
[RIN]
Shota Nakagawa?
[NAKAGAWA]
Here!
[RIN]
Kazuki Minami?
[MINAMI]
Here!
[RIN]
Dai Ryono?
[RYONO]
Yo!
[RIN]
You guys are on Freestyle relay.
Next up, medley roster.
Backstroke, Momotaro Mikoshiba.
Awesome!
[RIN]
Breaststroke.
Aiichirou Nitori.
--Yes, sir! Thank you!
--[SAMEZUKA CLUB] Whoa...
[RIN]
Butterfly, Sosuke Yamazaki.
Yeah.
'Course, yours truly will
cover the individual Freestyle.
No partying tonight,
I want all of you to rest.
Dismissed.
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Yes, sir!
What'd I say, man?
You were a shoe-in
for the relay team!
Thanks! Congratulations!
[RIN]
Sosuke.
Tomorrow, no regrets
either way. Right?
[SOSUKE]
No regrets.
Hey, uh. Haru?
You see a towel in there?
Hello?
[BELLHOP 9A]
Excuse me.
[BELLHOP 9A yelps]
[SOSUKE gasps, grunts]
[BELLHOP 9A]
I'm so sorry!
[SOSUKE grunts]
[HARUKA] That shoulder
still giving you grief?
What's that supposed to mean?
[HARUKA]
Drop the act.
I saw Kisumi the other day.
Tch. Good for you.
[HARUKA]
Hang on.
[SOSUKE] Not like it's gonna
make any difference tomorrow,
but... tell Rin, and you
an' me have a problem.
[MAKOTO laughs]
So how long's he
been gone, exactly?
I dunno, he snuck off
while I was in the shower.
You know him, he's probably
out jogging or whatever.
[RIN]
Ugh. Great.
The entire place is crawling
with college scouts.
Of all nights to go MIA.
That guy is such a loose cannon.
So, d'you want to talk to
him about something, or...?
[RIN] Yeah, I want to
ask him if he's decided
what he wants to do yet.
Guess he's just
running away, as usual.
Big shock there.
What is he thinking?
[MAKOTO] I wouldn't
read too much into it.
With some people, it's just
how they clear their heads.
He's more of a doer,
than a talker.
[RIN sighs] Well, that's a
polite way of puttin' it.
[MAKOTO laughs]
Okay. Enough about him.
What's the story with you?
[MAKOTO]
Uh?
Look, there's no reason
a swimmer at your level
wouldn't be scouted by at
least a second tier school.
[MAKOTO]
Well...
[knocking]
[NAGISA]
Hey guys, you've seriously gotta
check this out--
[NAGISA, REI]
Rin?
Do none of you people
even care that we're
swimming Regionals
tomorrow? Go to bed!
[NAGISA]
Ow!
Cut us some slack,
it's barely eleven.
[REI]
Is everything all right, or...?
[RIN] I just dropped by
to see Haru for a minute.
But I mean,
he's out doing whatever,
so I guess I'll have
to wait. Goodnight.
[NAGISA]
Hey, hold up.
Tomorrow, you're goin' down.
Now that's the
attitude I wanna see.
[HARUKA panting]
[PRINCIPAL 9A]
Every member of the faculty
is as thrilled as can be!
Do your school proud.
[TODOU] Can't let that
talent go to waste.
You'll have lots of eyes
on you in tomorrow's race.
[CROWD cheering]
[HARUKA]
I can't see.
The big moment's finally here.
[HARUKA]
What are you talking about?
This is what we trained for!
The best part is,
there's no telling how many
scouts'll be watching
us out there!
[HARUKA]
Good for them.
[REI] Theoretically speaking,
given the waves you've made
at District, it's a
well-nigh impossibility
to slip under their radar.
You've got this!
[HARUKA]
I get it. Stop.
[NITORI] We're prepared
to be wowed by you, Nanase!
Good luck!
Get in the pool.
[AMAKATA] There's an old
saying that's appropriate.
"Run all you want.
Our problems always know exactly
where to find us in the end."
[GOU]
Haruka.
My brother's really looking
forward to this match.
[RIN]
What are you waitin' for?
It's now or never.
[CROWD cheering]
[HARUKA]
Huh?
[CROWD cheering]
[HARUKA panting]
[REFEREE 9A]
On your marks!
[HARUKA]
Huh?
[TODOU]
That's it, kid.
We're all here for you,
give us the goods!
Show us freedom!
[HARUKA yells]
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA pants]
[MAKOTO breathing heavily]
This is gonna be so cool!
Yes, well, and nerve-wracking.
You okay, Haru? Hey.
It's nothing, I'm fine.
[HANAMURA] Have no fear,
your cheerleaders are here!
[GOU laughs]
Hana!
[STUDENT 9A] We got up at the
butt-crack of dawn for this.
[STUDENT 9B]
Totally worth it, though.
We'll try not to
let you girls down.
[REI]
Um. Why isn't Sasabe here?
[AMAKATA]
Oh, right.
He sends his apologies,
the Swim Club was too busy
for him to make it.
[NAGISA]
Aw! Lamest excuse ever!
[SWIMMER 9A]
Check it out: University scouts.
All over the place.
How do you spell that?
I'm not sure.
[SWIMMER 9B]
There's a ton of 'em, huh?
[GUY 9C]
No kidding.
Just bear in mind,
the outside lane is hardest.
This is the real deal.
It's probably best if we
divide and conquer at first.
[MAKOTO]
Haru?
Hey. Earth to Haru?
[HARUKA gasps]
Huh?
You sure you're all right, man?
Uh... Stop asking me.
I told you, I'm good.
It's just about that time.
Let's win this thing!
Good luck you guys!
Go kick some butt!
[REI, NAGISA]
Yeah!
[MAKOTO]
Okay.
I guess this is
the moment of truth.
So let's give it our best.
[REI, NAGISA chuckle]
[REI, NAGISA]
Right!
[MOMOTARO]
Stag beetle!
[MIKOSHIBA, MOMOTARO grunt]
Ow! What the heck?
Oh, hey big bro!
Whatcha got there,
your relay order sheet?
Here. Let's have a lil' look.
Hey! Come on, you're
not 'sposed to see that!
You're on the roster! Nice!
Duh, 'course I am.
What else they gonna do
with the guy who slayed
your backstroke record?
So this is Matsuoka's idea
of an ideal team, huh?
Ideal? What're you
talkin' about?
All right, people! Pony up!
We got a reputation to spread!
Let's show them all how an
ideal relay team does it!
[RIN]
Glad you decided to join us.
Now what are you
babbling about?
I ran into my brother!
He told me all about last year!
I know about the tournament!
[GROUP gasps]
[MOMOTARO] Sounds like something
out of a cheesy movie, yeah,
but the fact is, when
you guys got together,
miracles happened,
plain and simple!
It's the best story ever!
Seriously it almost made me cry!
I want that! I want a
team like you guys had!
[GROUP chuckles]
[RIN] Look, I'm flattered
but you gotta take it easy.
That was last year. We need
to focus on the present.
Let's do some exchanges
in the warm-up pool.
[MOMOTARO]
Yeah! I'm all about it!
Teamwork! C'mon, Nitori!
[NITORI]
Actually, I'm uh.
I'm kinda starting to
get a little nervous.
[SOSUKE] Easy, champ.
It's just a warm-up.
[MOMOTARO, NITORI laugh]
[RIN]
All right, let's do this!
[NITORI, MOMOTARO]
Yeah!
[SOSUKE grunts]
[RIN gasps]
[RIN]
What was that about?
Sorry. My bad.
Got distracted, screwed up.
You got "distracted?"
Yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna go take five
and grab a soda.
[ANNOUNCER 9A] Men's
one-hundred meter backstroke,
third heat, begins now!
[REI, GOU]
Go for it, Makoto!
It's all you, come on!
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 9A]
Ready...
[beep]
[CROWD] Go!
[GOU] Let's go, let's go, let's
go, let's go, let's go Makoto!
[IWATOBI CLUB] Let's go,
let's go, let's go, let's go,
let's go Makoto!
[GOU] Push it, push it, push it,
push it, push it Makoto!
[IWATOBI CLUB] Push it,
push it, push it, push it,
push it Makoto!!
[GOU]
Last lap, go!
[IWATOBI CLUB]
[GOU]
Last lap, go!
[IWATOBI CLUB]
Last lap, go! Last lap, go!
Yeah!
This is a totally
different animal
than District, evidently.
[NAGISA]
You can say that again.
[RIN] Sucks Makoto didn't
make it to the finals,
I thought he had a shot.
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
[RIN]
So. Have you made a decision?
[HARUKA]
Not really.
What the heck's your problem?
You saw how many top tier
scouts came out of the woodwork
after District. I couldn't
get a moment's peace.
If they came for me,
they came for you.
Whatever.
I'll hit you up on this
again after the race.
Good luck out there.
[ANNOUNCER 9A] The men's
one-hundred-meter Freestyle,
fifth heat, begins now!
[GOU]
Go, Rin!
No offense, but I'm
rather glad Haru and Rin
are in different heats for this
one, who can take that tension?
[NAGISA]
Haru's in the next one.
Hey, welcome back.
Nice work out there.
Thanks a lot, guys.
Rin's about to jump in
for the Freestyle fifth heat.
[REFEREE 9A]
Ready...
[beep]
[CROWD] Go!
[SAMEZUKA 9C]
And... Fight!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB] Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Come on! Fight!
[MAKOTO] That's incredible!
He's already taken the lead!
[REI]
Here comes the turn!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
One down!
[MAKOTO]
Wow. Still way out ahead!
[NAGISA]
Look at him!
Guy's so fast, he's like
a friggin' torpedo!
[REI]
Outstanding!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Yeah!
Oh yeah!
If this were the finals,
that time would win
him the whole thing!
So then, he definitely
made it to finals, yeah?
--[UOZUMI] Yeah, man.
--[MINAMI] Ha! Of course!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
All right, all right, Samezuka!
All right!
[ANNOUNCER 9A]
Next, we have the men's
one hundred-meter
freestyle, sixth heat.
I have a feeling
Haru's gonna wow us.
[HARUKA gasps]
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 9A]
Ready...
[beep]
[CROWD] Go!
[HARUKA panting]
[HARUKA panting heavily]
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA grunting]
[HARUKA]
No.
[MIKOSHIBA, TODOU gasp]
[MOMOTARO, NITORI gasp]
[CROWD murmuring]
What's happening?
What's he doing?
[RIN]
Haru!
What was that?
Are you out of your mind?
[HARUKA]
Like it's any of your business.
[RIN]
What?
Do you realize how many
scouts just saw you tank?
Why should I care about them?
[RIN gasps]
[HARUKA]
Who are they to me?
What is any of this to me?
You think I do this
for the crowds, or so I can say
"Hey, look at my awesome time?"
Why do you do it, then?
I swim for myself.
And my friends.
[GROUP gasps]
Then you owe it to them and
yourself to give a care!
At least give 'em the
benefit of the doubt!
You have something here!
If you'd just take it seriously
for once in your life!
You think your friends
wanna stand there
and watch you piss
away your future?
[HARUKA grunts]
[RIN gasps]
No one asked you to
care about my future!
What "future?" What is it
you think I have?
This is my life, not yours!
I'm not you!
I'm never going to be you!
[MAKOTO]
Haru...
[REI]
You didn't mean any of that...?
How long have you guys
been standing there?
[HARUKA]
Listen. It's okay.
We're a team. And I'm
still gonna swim relay.
I didn't come this far not to.
[SOSUKE panting, sobbing]
[SOSUKE] Why couldn't we
have stayed kids forever?
It's so much harder
holding on to your dreams
once the world gets
its hooks into you.
[RIN]
What are you talking about?
If you're dreaming,
you must be asleep.
Wake up, man!
It's time to make
those dreams real.
Next time:
"Six-Beat of Tears!"
[SOSUKE]
Hey, Rin.
Be honest with me: you still
want the same things out of life
you did when we were little?