[doorbell rings]
[MAKOTO] Haru!
That's weird.
Is he taking a cold bath again?
I haven't seen him do that
since summer started.
Hey. Coming in, bro.
Uh, how long are you
plannin' to marinate
in that tub? Come on, let's go.
[MAKOTO gasps]
[NAGISA]
You're mine, Makoto!
[MAKOTO screams]
[MAKOTO]
Dude...
You really scared the
crap out of me back there.
[NAGISA giggles]
I couldn't help myself. Sorry.
[MAKOTO]
Yes, you could've!
[REI]
I'm confused.
What were you doing
at Haru's place?
[MAKOTO] I think he slept
over there last night.
Isn't that right?
[HARUKA]
Hm? Oh. Uh, yeah, he did.
[banging]
[HARUKA]
Not bad.
[banging]
[NAGISA grunting]
[NAGISA]
Aw! I bent it again!
Oh well.
[NAGISA]
That's what I'm talkin' about!
Hm.
Ah! Here it is!
Bam! En guard!
--Nagisa.
--Ah! Uh. Hi, Haru!
What are you doing here?
[NAGISA]
Huh?
Uh... Ha, ha. Um,
Well, I'm here to see
the Leonid meteor shower!
That's fine, but you
really shouldn't
start a fire out here.
Oh. Of course. Silly me.
[HARUKA] So I decided to
let him stay the night.
Yeah, it was really nice of him.
The Leonid Media Shower's
not 'til the fall though.
Huh? Oh!
Must've had my dates wrong.
That's classic me!
Guys.
How 'bout stepping things up
at practice today?
I figure if we work harder
it can only increase
our chances of winning.
Are you in?
Uh--
[REI]
Uh...
[NAGISA] Like they say:
"practice makes perfect!"
[RIN panting]
[NITORI]
Good work out there!
[RIN]
Thanks.
What is it, Sosuke?
Well, you look more toned
than you normally do.
You're right, he does.
[RIN]
Oh, yeah.
I'm trying out a new
training regimen,
seems to be working
out pretty well.
So cool!
Someone as good as you
keeps trying to get better!
'Course I do. Always.
You don't put in the time,
you don't get
to the international level.
Right, Sosuke?
Uh. Yeah. That's right.
[MOMOTARO gurgling]
Hey, look at me!
Check it out, you guys!
I'm doing it! I'm really
doing the backstroke!
[UOZUMI]
Ow! What's your deal?
[RIN] What do I hate more,
his swimming or his talking?
[AMAKATA] All right, let's
leave it at that for today!
[IWATOBI CLUB]
Great job, everybody!
[MAKOTO] Wow, I can't believe
how late it is already.
Ugh, my arms feel like Jelly
from paddling so hard today.
[MAKOTO laughs] You'll get
used to it after a while.
But, It looks like
Haru likes fin practice
better than paddling.
Uh. Wait, Fin?
It's a flipper for your foot.
O-Oh right, of course.
[MAKOTO]
Well, Haru?
[HARUKA]
Not really.
[REI]
Hey, Nagisa?
[NAGISA grunts]
Yeah. What's up?
How come you're staring
off into space like that?
What's wrong, man, are you
just tired or somethin'?
Uh. Yeah. I'm pretty wiped.
Well, you're the one
who was all gung-ho
about us pushing
ourselves, my friend.
You have no right to
complain about being tired.
Well, why not? I get tired!
Uh-- You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine!
Oh! I just remembered I forgot
something in the clubroom!
You guys go ahead without me!
See you tomorrow!
Hey! Wait a second!
[MAKOTO] This scene is
lookin' pretty familiar.
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
[REI]
What are you talking about?
[MAKOTO]
Oh, never mind.
But something is definitely
wrong with him.
And he clearly
doesn't want to talk.
Yeah. Whatever it is,
I just hope he doesn't try
to push all of us away.
[HARUKA]
A little too sweet.
[doorbell rings]
[HARUKA]
Yes?
Haru! Uh, I--
I came to visit you!
[HARUKA]
Huh?
Barley tea, okay?
Yeah, it's perfect.
[NAGISA]
Is this your future academic
and career plans worksheet?
Can I look at it?
[HARUKA]
Whatever.
[NAGISA chuckles]
That's just like you, Haru!
Reminds me, I was
supposed to turn mine in
already, but I
haven't started yet.
[HARUKA] Have you already
decided what you wanna do?
[NAGISA]
Hm!
Oh.
[NAGISA]
Three things.
I want to be a penguin keeper.
A treasure hunter.
Or a deep sea explorer.
But, I also want
to travel the world,
so a tour guide would be
a pretty awesome job.
Ugh. It's not fair that we
have to choose just one thing.
[HARUKA] Hm. So, that's your
version of "decided," huh?
[NAGISA giggles]
[CATS meow]
[HARUKA] Well, I bet you can
become anything you want.
[NAGISA]
Thanks.
Hey, the same thing
goes for you.
You're smart.
You're a great cook.
You're good with your hands too.
And you're a really
talented artist.
[NAGISA]
I wish I was lucky enough
to be as versatile as you.
Not to mention, you're the
best swimmer I've ever seen!
I bet you could be a
pro swimmer if you wanted to!
[HARUKA]
No thanks.
Wha...?
I guess I should've
expected that.
[HARUKA]
Well?
[NAGISA]
Huh?
[HARUKA] You gonna tell me
why you came to my house
in the middle of the night?
Oh! Uh...
Well, I told ya, I'm here
for the meteor shower.
Yeah, but it's not
until the fall.
Uh. No, you're right.
What's up?
Ah! Well, I'd better go.
So, uh. Thanks a
lot for having me.
Ah! Hey! Wait!
[NAGISA]
Hi, Mako!
Do you wanna hang out?
[MAKOTO]
But, Nagisa...
It's the middle of the night.
[NAGISA] You know what they say:
no time like the present!
[MAKOTO]
Uh-- Haru?
[NAGISA gasps]
Dude, tell us what happened.
[HARUKA, MAKOTO]
You ran away?
[NAGISA]
Yeah.
Why'd you do it?
[NAGISA]
Just 'cause.
Please don't ask me anything
else, I just wanna stay over!
Come on!
[MAKOTO]
Mm... I can't.
But why not?
You can't stay over
without telling us why,
I'm sorry but it's
just the way it is.
[NAGISA]
Come on, Haru.
Don't be like that!
Look, we said "no,"
and we meant it. So--
[NAGISA]
Please!
Please...
[HARUKA]
Yes. Bye.
[MAKOTO sighs]
Were you on the phone?
Yeah. How is he?
Not good.
He still doesn't want
to talk about anything.
Ah! Hey guys!
Where is Nagisa?
I want to see him
right this instant!
Rei. Just calm down, okay?
[REI]
Fine. Where is he?
Don't worry. He's all right.
He's in the living room.
[MAKOTO] The bad news is,
he doesn't wanna
tell us what happened.
I'm guessing he's been
gone since yesterday.
[HARUKA]
Yeah, you're probably right.
[REI]
This is insane.
But I suppose it
does explain why
he's been acting
so strange lately.
[MAKOTO]
You know what's weird?
He never talks about his family.
[REI]
Yeah, that's true.
[HARUKA] I've never even heard
him mention them before.
[MAKOTO sighs]
Well, standing around waiting
isn't gonna do us any good.
I'll go see if I
can get him to talk.
He'll probably be more
comfortable if we have
the conversation
one on one, don't you think?
That's a great idea.
We'll leave the
talking to you, Makoto.
Here's hoping it goes well.
Thanks.
[MAKOTO]
Nagisa. I'm comin' in.
I feel bad for Nagisa! Dudes!
He said he's being taken away
to the supercountry Pangea!
We can't just let him go!
We have to do
something, you guys!
What are you talking about?
That's not even a real place!
[MAKOTO]
Huh? It's not?
Of course not!
How can you let him
trick you like that?
--I was tricked?!
--Yes!
[HARUKA sighs]
All right, it's my turn.
Uh-- Huh?
Good luck, Haru.
You're our only hope.
[HARUKA]
Nagisa. Pull up some floor.
I've decided to
let him stay with me.
Dude, why did you
let him bribe you?
Argh.
I can't trust you guys
to handle anything!
I'll take care of this.
No one can resist my enhanced
negotiation techniques.
Back in a flash.
Rei.
I'm not Rei.
You guys can call me
"The Negotiator."
I know who's to blame.
You're welcome!
[MAKOTO]
For what?
[HARUKA]
Please. Tell us what's going on.
Yeah, why would you
decide to run away?
[MAKOTO sighs]
We're all just
really worried
about you, Nagisa.
We can't help you if you
won't tell us what happened.
He's right.
[NAGISA]
Mako. Haru...
I don't understand, is the
problem that you don't trust us?
Ngh! No!
[NAGISA]
You guys,
I'm sorry to make you
worry about me.
You're right.
You deserve to know.
The truth is...
See.
Because of some personal issues,
I might be forced
to quit the Swim Club.
[REI, HARUKA, MAKOTO gasp]
I don't understand.
The thing is, my grades
were pretty horrendous
on my midterm exams.
My mom and dad are extremely
strict about academic stuff.
So they told me I had
to give up swimming.
I can't just quit Swim Club
though. I love it too much.
So I decided to pack my things
and run away from home.
Well, what if you got
your grades back up?
Then you wouldn't
have to quit, right?
That's no big deal.
I'll help you study till
you're back on track.
You can tell your parents that!
Look, you don't get it,
once my parents
have their mind made up.
They don't go back on it,
no matter what.
But, if you just sit down
and try to talk to them--
[NAGISA] They won't listen
to me, they never do!
Seriously?
[MAKOTO]
C'mon.
There's gotta be another way.
[NAGISA]
Yeah.
I don't know what else
to do, though.
[REI]
Nagisa...
I guess by you running off
like this, you're hoping they'll
change their mind
about you swimming?
That's what you're
thinking, am I right?
Yeah.
Rei?
I'm sorry, but there's
no way that's going to work.
We need to seek out
other options.
I don't necessarily know
what those might be,
but I know this isn't feasible.
Even if you could get them to
let you stay in the Swim Club,
you wouldn't be at your
best living like this!
[NAGISA gasps]
All right. Let's leave
it at that.
[phone chimes]
[NAGISA gasps]
What is it?
It's from my sister.
She says that my mom
is coming here to bring me home!
[REI, MAKOTO gasp]
I'm freaking out!
What do I do?
This is bad!
We have to come up with a plan
and we have to do it quickly!
Guys, what if she forces
me to come home now?
[HARUKA] For the time being,
let's all just calm down.
Haru?
Come on.
[MAKOTO] Guess this is the
only place we have left to go.
[REI] Yeah, it's not like
we can go to school.
[MAKOTO]
You're right about that.
Good thing we got a key.
I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to get
you involved in this.
Don't be sorry.
Little too late for that.
Indeed.
What matters now is that
we stick together.
[HARUKA] We'd better keep
moving, we could be seen here.
[REI] True, we should head
to the locker rooms
where it's safe.
[MAKOTO]
What? No! No way!
It's so dark and scary!
That place could be haunted!
Don't be ridiculous.
You know ghosts aren't real!
Way to go, if there is a ghost,
you probably just
pissed him off!
[HARUKA]
Makoto, keep your voice down.
[MAKOTO]
Oops. My bad.
[REI] Let's hide here instead,
it's our smartest option.
All right. Here's the deal.
In order to get out of this,
you need to improve your grades.
And then hope for the best.
Uh. Yeah, that would be
the standard plan of attack.
[REI]
Level with me here.
How bad were your grades
that your parents were
gonna make you quit?
That one is good.
But the rest are atrocious.
[NAGISA laughs nervously]
[MAKOTO groans]
[MAKOTO]
Hey.
Didn't you go to a private
school for junior high?
[NAGISA]
Yeah. It was a prep school.
[REI]
And you know.
I don't remember your
grades being this bad
when we were freshman together.
So what's the deal?
I don't know.
[NAGISA] It's probably
because I hate studying.
[REI]
You hate it?
I bet you just weren't
focused enough.
[NAGISA]
No, that's not it.
Before I ran away,
I was miserable.
[NAGISA] The only reason
I took the junior high exams
in the first place, is because
my parents forced me.
They decided I should continue
on with my education so I could
get into a college and get
a steady, dependable job.
That's just how things
are at my house.
You study, you to college,
you get a job.
When I was in junior high,
they made me study all the time.
But there wasn't a
single thing fun about it.
After a while,
I lost sight of why
I was studying to begin with.
I just couldn't focus, y'know?
Studying became like
some kind of torture.
My parents couldn't stand
to see me like that.
So they sent me to Iwatobi
hoping I'd snap out of it.
Which turned out to be a
blessing in disguise because
I was able to swim
whenever I wanted.
Yeah, but why Iwatobi?
[HARUKA] I mean, it's not like
we're the only school around
that has a Swimming Club, right?
[NAGISA]
Well... That's an easy one.
I wanted to be at
Iwatobi so I could swim
with you and Haru again.
And then, I met Rei,
and that made swimming
that much more of a pleasure.
For me, swimming's
the highlight of my day.
It's the only part of my
life that makes sense.
It's my one true joy.
[NAGISA] But when my parents
told me I had to quit,
I lost my mind.
It's like I couldn't
think straight anymore.
Just the thought of having
to go back to my life
the way it was before
honestly terrified me.
So that's why you
decided to run away?
[NAGISA]
Yeah.
[REI] Have you told your
parents this, Nagisa?
Do they know how you
really feel about it?
Huh? No, they don't.
I haven't told them yet because
I don't think they would listen.
[car revving]
[REI gasps]
--[NAGISA, MAKOTO gasp]
--This isn't good!
Maybe it's not your mom!
No way, who else would be
coming here at this hour?
Either way, we need to get
out of Dodge, right now!
[NAGISA, MAKOTO gasp]
[MAKOTO]
We should hide you.
[REI]
Quick. Let's go!
Haru! Come on!
Yeah.
Are you guys sure
we'll be safe here?
Hope so.
Do you really think
it's my mom?
Shh. Be quiet.
[footsteps scuffing]
[ALL sigh]
[MAKOTO]
Quick, let's head for the pool!
[MAKOTO] We're good, no one
would come all the way in here.
[NAGISA]
Yeah.
[MAKOTO]
Hey, Rei. You all right?
Uh--
[REI] I'm fine, it's just
there's something
I really need to
ask you, Nagisa.
[NAGISA]
What is it?
[REI] Correct me if I'm wrong,
but you didn't think
your parents would
understand how important
Swim Club was to you?
Well, here's the thing.
Is it fair to give up
talking to them
until you've actually tried?
[NAGISA gasps]
[REI] No matter how
hopeless things might seem,
if you just try, well,
you'll be surprised
what you can accomplish.
When you were sad,
you didn't give up.
Why would you give up now?
Are you just gonna be a quitter?
Rei, take it easy.
I-- I don't wanna give up.
No.
Good then.
Say it proudly and
do something about it!
[MAKOTO]
Guys. This isn't the time, okay?
Tell them the truth.
Go get what you want.
Rei. You don't understand.
You don't know
what it's like for me!
You have no idea.
[REI]
No, you're right.
As far as your home
life goes, I don't know.
But I do know I want
to swim with my friends.
And I want to swim with you!
Rei...
[REI]
I love it just like you, Nagisa.
I couldn't stand to lose
the thing we both love
more than anything else
in the world without a fight.
Don't you want to swim?
Of course I do!
[REI] Good. I didn't think
you were the type of person
who would give up that easily.
[NAGISA gasps]
[REI] No matter how many
times I turned you down,
you wouldn't give up.
You kept inviting me to join
the Swim Club till I agreed.
Rei, I...
Don't you see?
Giving up is the
last thing I wanna do.
I wanna keep swimming.
I wanna swim with you guys!
I just want to be free!
Okay. Let's all work together
to come up with a solid plan
that'll convince your parents
to see your side.
Well, what do you say team?
Are you with me or not?
[clattering]
Oh no!
I can't believe
they came so far in.
Guys! Our backs are
against the wall here.
We haven't had enough time!
[HARUKA]
Nagisa, go hide somewhere!
[MAKOTO] There isn't anywhere
to hide, we're next to the pool!
Hey.
You can stand behind my back,
but you gotta hurry up!
[REI] Don't worry,
we'll handle this somehow!
[HARUKA]
Nagisa!
[NAGISA]
Everyone, thank you.
But, I'm done running.
Wait, what?
[NAGISA inhales]
Mom!
I tried to hold it in, but I
can't keep silent anymore!
I always did what I was told!
But no matter what,
it was never fun!
The reason I ran away is
because I'm weak and afraid!
Too afraid to be
honest with you!
I know that it was
wrong of me to give up
before I ever tried.
So, from now on, I'm not gonna
run away from my problems!
I'm gonna face them!
No matter what!
[NAGISA]
Haru...
Mako...
And Rei, too.
I wanna swim with them!
Let me swim with my friends!
Mother!
I want you to listen
to what I say-- Uh?
[NAGISA, REI, MAKOTO gasp]
[MAKOTO]
It's Miss Amakata.
[AMAKATA]
Mr. Hazuki.
There is a very old saying.
"Raising children isn't easy."
[AMAKATA] Your parents
are worried about you.
Go see them.
[AMAKATA]
Sorry, everyone.
My timing was a little
awkward, wasn't it?
I'm confused,
how did you even know?
She knows 'cause I told her.
[MAKOTO]
What?
Yeah, he called and
told me what was going on.
He also assured me you'd take
care of Nagisa 'til I arrived.
Haru...
I'm sneaky.
[REI, MAKOTO laugh]
[HARUKA] But when the
car first pulled up,
I honestly wasn't
sure who it was.
Thanks a lot.
Listen to me.
You need to confront your
parents in a kind manner
and tell them how you feel.
And if that doesn't work?
Then, we'll figure
something out.
I'll tell them!
[MAKOTO]
Well. Should we go?
[HARUKA]
Sounds good.
[NAGISA]
Huh?
Are you coming or not?
You are gonna tell
your parents, aren't you?
Uh. Well yeah, I am.
[REI] What they're
trying to say is that
we're gonna go with you.
I mean let's be honest,
it's not like we can afford
to lose any Swim Club members.
Besides. You're the person
who forced me to join
the Swim Club in the
first place, remember?
You can't quit. I won't let you.
[MAKOTO]
C'mon, let's go.
[HARUKA]
You coming?
Uh. Right. Wait for me, guys!
[GOU gasps]
That happened?
[NAGISA]
Sorry I didn't tell ya.
I was in a bad way.
I'm just glad it worked out.
You were honest
with your parents
and so they let you stay
on the Swim Club.
[NAGISA] Mm-hm! Well,
that's only because I agreed
to study harder from now on.
Plus, they want me to go
to Nationals 'cause they realize
how important it is to me now.
Who knows, maybe I'll
surprise everyone
this time around?
I guess that means
we're gonna have to
work our butts off, huh?
Certainly sounds like it!
You can count me in.
[NAGISA]
All right then.
Lets get fired up and practice!
Nationals, we're on our way!
[IWATOBI CLUB]
Yeah!
[BIRD 5A whisles]
[RIN] It's finally time for
the District tournament.
Let's all do our best!
What's wrong, Rei?
[REI] Haru won't let go of
those cans of mackerel.
[HARUKA] These are no
ordinary mackerel cans.
These are legendary cans which
use fresh mackerel, line-caught
on the border of the Pacific
Ocean and the Seto Inland Sea!
[RIN]
Give 'em here!
[HARUKA grunts]
[RIN] Next time:
"Prime of Invincibility!"
[HARUKA]
Give them back, Rin!
[RIN] Haru, I'll tell you the
real legend of canned mackerel!
Trust me on that one!