[HARUKA]
Water.
A living thing.
You dive in,
and it bares its fangs.
It's hungry. Territorial.
Unless, of course, we're
talkin' ordinary tap water.
With that, you don't
feel much of anything.
Besides wet.
Give me a pool any day.
[MAKOTO]
Where-- Ah!
[MAKOTO 'Right, Ms. Tamura,
I'm out. Have a good one.
[TAMURA]
You too, Makoto.
Tell Haruka I said hello.
And here, take this.
[MAKOTO] Oh, wow, really?
You didn't have to do that.
Thank you!
[MAKOTO] Okay, okay.
Just for a second, though.
Yep. Spring's in the air.
[doorbell rings]
Of course.
[MAKOTO] It's me, dude.
I'm coming in.
[MAKOTO]
You in here?
This where you sleep?
Good morning, Haruka--
I thought we agreed
not to call me that.
Sorry, Haru. Old habit.
[MAKOTO]
Seriously?
There a problem?
Nothing.
Somebody didn't get
enough practice in
over winter break, huh?
You wanna step
it up a notch?
We're running late.
[HARUKA]
Fine.
I told the guys we'd meet
'em at the station-- Uh.
It's a little cold out
there for an apron!
[HARUKA] I need to
make my lunch, man.
Gimme a sec.
[MAKOTO] What part of "running
late" don't you understand?
[REI]
They should be here by now.
Ugh. Nagisa, please.
You're gonna give
yourself indigestion.
Try a bite, it's good.
Thanks, I'll pass.
How you frontload those calories
and still have room for lunch
I'll never know.
Eating machine!
[MAKOTO]
Nagisa! Rei!
I know, I know,
we suck, I'm sorry!
Yeah!
That's right!
Ain't nobody can take me!
[GOU]
Yo! Over here, guys!
Is this the big
farewell meet?
Yup.
Seems a little
bit excessive.
They go at it 'til
they drop, or what?
[RIN]
Samezuka tradition.
We swim the hundred meter 'til
one of us beats the captain.
Rin.
Good to see you guys.
Glad you could make it.
[NAGISA] Hey, Rin!
Did we miss your race?
No, you're good.
[REI] Not to be
the naysayer,
but exhausting
yourselves like this
strikes me a little irrational.
Yeah, well, rational isn't
Captain Mikoshiba's MO.
[REI]
Heh. I suppose not.
Hey-hey! You decided
to show up, huh?
C'mon! Dive in
for old times' sake!
We're cool, thanks.
Yeah. We're just here
to observe and admire.
Screw that!
Four-hundred meter freestyle,
Iwatobi versus Samezuka,
all or nothing!
Matsuoka, show 'em how we do!
Right...
[MIKOSHIBA]
Anyone else not dead?
Me!
[MIKOSHIBA]
Nitori! Excellent!
We're not really prepared!
We're moral support, that's it!
[NAKAGAWA]
Yes, sir!
[MAKOTO]
Oh, no.
[GOU] Ah! Look at those tricep
brachii stand at attention!
Does the man
never wear boxers?
Well, if you
can't beat 'em...
...keep swimming!
[REI]
Do what?
[NAGISA]
Ta-da!
[REI] Why the hell would you
have your swimsuits packed?
Just a vibe I was getting
off of Haru last night.
We had an understanding!
No worries, my friend, we can
accommodate you. Nitori.
[NITORI]
Sir!
What is that
supposed to mean?
No, wait! I don't need
to be accommodated!
[GOU]
Samezuka versus Iwatobi.
Four-hundred meter
freestyle relay.
Ready.
Set!
[whistle blows]
[CROWD cheers]
Makoto, way to go.
Wow, look!
He's already taken the lead!
[REI] The speed on that
front-crawl is spectacular.
Get ready
to lose. Aye-aye!
Ugh. Please stop
calling me that.
What do you know,
it's my turn already.
[RIN]
Ai.
[NITORI gasps]
Don't be so tense.
Okay.
Idiot's bending his knees
like a chicken.
[MIKOSHIBA]
I'm next.
Huh?
[MIKOSHIBA] Bring it home
for us, Matsuoka.
You got it, sir.
[AMAKATA]
Since when has Ryugazaki
been comfortable
swimming freestyle?
Since never, actually.
[AMAKATA] Uh. This is
a freestyle relay, right?
[GOU]
Uh huh.
My area of expertise...
is the butterfly!
Wait, is he allowed
to do that?
Sure! That's the whole point
of calling it freestyle!
[MIKOSHIBA] Oh yeah?
Well, two can play at that game!
[CROWD cheers]
[MAKOTO]
They're closing the gap!
[NAGISA] Crap! His goggles
are slipping off again!
Pull through, Rei!
You can do it!
[MAKOTO]
You got this!
[NITORI, ORANGE TRUNKS SWIMMER]
Come on, Captain!
Hey, it just dawned on me
this is our first legit
relay against each other.
Yeah?
It's a real shame you guys're
about to lose it, y'know.
Too bad I don't
really care who wins.
Whatever.
[NAGISA]
Yeah!
[MAKOTO]
Rei!
Almost there!
Woo!
Aw!
We got our butts kicked!
Victory was so close
I could taste it!
[MAKOTO chuckles]
The important thing
is we all had fun.
No question there.
[MIKOSHIBA]
Good teamwork.
I'm proud of ya.
This is the part where
we Third Years bow out.
No tears. No regrets.
Look alive!
It ain't gonna be a pool
party after I'm gone!
Come April, you'll have
a world-class athlete
settin' the pace!
I advise you to enjoy the slack
while you can, ladies!
He really turns on
a dime, doesn't he?
[MIKOSHIBA]
Matsuoka.
Yes, sir.
Starting tomorrow morning,
you call the shots.
[RIN exhales]
That means you're
the new captain.
[RIN inhales]
[RIN]
Yes, sir.
[applause]
I didn't see
that one coming.
Rin's far from
the obvious choice
for Mikoshiba's replacement.
Are you crazy?
His body's in top shape!
If that's not a captain's
physique, I don't know what is!
[MAKOTO laughs]
[REI] No one's saying
he doesn't look fantastic.
[FILM CLUB 1A] Iwatobi High's
Film Club proudly presents:
a masterpiece for the ages.
[FILM CLUB 1B]
Ten years in the making.
[FILM CLUB 1C] Just when you
thought it was safe to cosplay.
What the--?
[GOU] Hey, I need you
back here with us.
Ugh. I'm telling ya,
we should've just made
an action movie,
apparently anyone can.
Right now really
isn't the ideal time
for expressing second thoughts.
[MAKOTO]
Don't be that way.
Guys, please, whatever
happens out there,
stay on script and we're golden.
Gou's not about
to steer us wrong.
Right.
[FILM CLUB MEMBERS] Join us to
become a more fabulous you!
[ANNOUNCER 1A] Next up,
we have the Swim Club.
I'm not saying we're the
coolest club in school.
I'm not even saying
we're the best.
We're just the people
who got it in our heads
last spring to fix your pool!
I'm Gou Matsuoka, club manager.
And this... is our treasurer!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[NAGISA]
Nagisa Hazuki, Second Year!
I'm a breaststroke man and
my best feature is my soleus.
Ladies.
[GOU]
Vice Captain!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[HARUKA]
Haruka Nanase, Third Year!
Freestyle is my thing,
and my triceps are guaranteed
to drive you out of your mind.
[GOU]
Secretary!
[REI]
Rei Ryugazaki, Second Year!
Butterfly expert, who when
asked his best feature
will answer that his deltoids
and biceps are in a dead heat.
[GOU]
And our team captain!
[MAKOTO]
Makoto Tachibana, Third Year!
I've got backstroke for days!
And traps just as long!
[GOU] Join us, and become
a more muscular you!
Alright, so where is everybody?
I told you we'd just
look cheap up there!
Couldn't we've been
tasteful and understated?
Don't start with me!
You got off on struttin'
your stuff and you know it!
Everybody calm down.
The show was fine,
it's just a bad time of
year for new recruits.
If they could see us swim,
they'd be here in droves.
[NAGISA] So you're tellin' me
there's nothing we can do
to drum up a little interest?
Bath toy plushies
of ourselves, maybe?
We're not going there.
We could have someone draw
us as comic book heroes?
We tried that
last year, remember?
We could always parade around in
our swimsuits twenty-four-seven.
[GOU]
Perfection!
Forget it!
[GOU]
Ugh, you're so lame!
[REI]
That's not the issue!
[NAKAGAWA]
Last twenty-five meters! Go!
[RIN] To make it on
the Samezuka Swim Team,
you need to beat the benchmark
time, no exceptions.
Pay attention to form.
Pick a style you feel
comfortable with
and show us what you've got.
Sir!
[RIN]
You're kidding me, right?
I can't be captain!
[MIKOSHIBA]
It's my call.
I'm not qualified. I mean,
leading the whole team...
[MIKOSHIBA]
Quit whinin'.
I thought you wanted this.
Well, I--
[MIKOSHIBA]
What was all that talk
about making this team
great? Man up, Rin.
Dude, this is me sayin'
I believe in you.
[NITORI]
You all right, sir?
You look a bit preoccupied.
[RIN] Ai. You really
gotta stop calling me sir.
[NITORI]
But--
Just drop it.
[NITORI]
Yes, si-- uh, okay.
There's a ton of people here.
I didn't know we'd
stirred up so much hype.
[RIN] Maybe they
wanna catch a glimpse
of the "world-class athlete"
Mikoshiba was talking about.
Do you think there's a chance
he's here right now?
I dunno, but keep
standing here
you might lose your
place to a First Year.
Oh! Right!
[AMAKATA]
Open the pool?
Yeah, so we can start
practice earlier!
And maybe in the process get
a few new members interested.
I get where you're
coming from,
but even if I could open it,
isn't it too cold?
The cold doesn't
bother me at all.
No reason swimming
can't be a winter sport.
[GROUP]
We're begging you, miss!
Boys, please!
Let me think for a moment.
[AMAKATA gasps]
What about Coach
Sasabe's indoor pool?
I think it's opening soon.
[SASABE]
Hm. I guess.
Huh? Oh, hey there!
You lookin' to join up?
I won't be operational
for another month,
but we're accepting
membership applications.
[SOSUKE]
No, thanks.
[SASABE] So, you scoping
the competition, or what?
The Iwatobi guys aren't here?
Someone told me this
is where they meet.
Huh? Ah, well.
That someone told you right.
See, developers were supposed
to turn this place into a spa.
But they went bankrupt
when the bubble burst.
Whole kit 'n' caboodle
was slated for demolition.
Golden opportunity
for me though.
I used the revenue from
my grandpa's squid boat
to buy this li'l piece o'
heaven and remodel it.
Labor of love, let me tell ya.
Before I met these kids,
no one would've taken me
for the kind of guy
to see a project
like this through,
but that's the moral, I guess:
live free, live bold,
devil take the hindmo--!
Oh. All righty, then.
[MAKOTO] Don't get me wrong,
Coach's place is nice.
I just think it's
good PR to clean out
our own pool first, y'know?
[REI] I agree. Even if
we can't fill it in yet,
at least we can still
make a good impression.
[GOU] Don't worry, Miss A
will come through for us.
We'll be up and
runnin' in no time.
[NAGISA] Betcha we're gonna
have so many new bloods
wantin' to join, this
place'll be crazy, yeah?
Hey, as long as they're
serious about swimming.
[NAGISA] You've gotta
learn to lighten up, man.
Watch the attitude. Please?
We don't want to
chase recruits off
before they've had
a chance to get wet,
the club's survival
hinges on numbers.
Relays aren't going to happen
with just the four of us.
Not everyone can
be as grim as you.
[SASABE]
Fresh-faced recruits, huh?
Well, the surefire way
to scare up interest
is to win some races.
[REI] Obviously, yes,
but easier said than done.
[MAKOTO] I'm sorry, Coach.
You needed us for something?
[SASABE laughs]
[SASABE] Nothing worthwhile
is ever easy, my friend.
But you do have
a hell of a resource!
[gasps]
[MAKOTO] The Iwatobi Swim Club
is back in business!
[SASABE] Yes it is!
I give you: Iwatobi SC Returns!
Say hello to months of
blood, sweat, tears, escrow,
and the perfect pH balance!
[NAGISA] You're the greatest
human being alive!
Yeah, thank you Coach!
Look, if you wanna thank me,
train hard and kick some tail at
next week's city tournament
like the champions
I know you to be!
Aw... Not so fast, chief!
[MAKOTO]
Haru, wait! He said--!
[splash]
Damn it! Listen when
people are talking to you!
Last one in's
a rotten egg!
[SASABE]
Fine! Use the locker room!
[RIN] Okay, well, since
it's a city tournament,
I guess we won't
make it mandatory
for everyone on the team to--
[NAGISA]
Rin!
[NAGISA laughs]
Ugh. As I was saying,
you don't have to go
if you don't want,
but it'd put some experience
under your belt.
Give it some thought.
[CLUB MEMBERS]
Right!
[REI]
What do you know?
The man makes a decent
captain after all.
"Rawr! Do or die, maggots!
Take no prisoners!"
That's my impression of what
he thinks he sounds like.
Now, that's not very nice.
[SASABE]
You're late!
[NAGISA] Whoa! Why're
you suited up, Coach?
Ha! 'Cause! There's a
gen pop category, too!
[AMAKATA] It's a much
more relaxed atmosphere
than the regionals.
Rather nice, if you ask me.
If you go for paunches and
underdeveloped muscles maybe.
Shame there's no relay for us
to showcase our teamwork.
Yeah, kinda sucks.
But there'll be relays
in the regionals, though.
[HARUKA]
Hey, man.
You hanging out for
the hell of it, or what?
Waitin' on you, man.
[RIN] We're in lanes
next to each other again.
[HARUKA]
I saw.
[RIN] Listen, since you guys
can't train in the winter,
it's only fair if
I give you a handicap.
Just say the word. I want
this race to be interesting.
[HARUKA]
We don't need your charity.
There are ways to
train without a pool.
[RIN chuckles]
[RIN] Sounds like an intense
off-season regimen.
You'll have to show it to me.
If you can catch up--
[BOY 1B]
You ready to go down?
[BOY 1C]
In your dreams, loser!
[BOY 1B]
Your mom's dreams!
[BOYS laugh]
[RIN and HARUKA chuckle]
[RIN]
No relay in this one, buddy.
Just us. Mano y mano.
It's not like I'm worried
about setting a record.
Still tryin' to play it off
like you don't really care?
Heh. Whatever.
Keep telling yourself that.
You may not care
about winning,
but you still think
you're the best.
You're too cool for
your own good, dude.
I'm gonna light
a fire under you.
[NAGISA]
Nice. Rin and Haru are up next.
[GOU]
C'mon, big bro!
[MAKOTO]
Haru!
[REI]
You can do it!
[MALE REFEREE 1A]
Ready...
[whistle blows]
Oh, wow, look
how fast they are!
[MAKOTO]
Rin's gaining the lead. Fast.
Don't get left behind. Haru!
--[REI] Push, push, push!
--[MAKOTO] C'mon!
[REI] They're on a whole
other level than the rest.
Oh, man! Haru sure is giving
Rin a run for his money!
They got the same time?
Incredible!
[ANNOUNCER 1A] Congratulations
to the swimmers in lanes
four and five!
Nanase and Matsuoka have set
our first tournament record!
[RIN]
Haru.
I knew you had
it in you, man.
You just needed fire.
Whatever you say.
[GOU] Way to go, Haru!
You were amazing!
You didn't just outdo yourself,
you tied with my brother!
[AMAKATA] I think you all
reached a new personal best.
[SASABE] Meh, I'd have done
better if I'd kept in shape.
[AMAKATA] Don't be
so hard on yourself.
What's that old saying?
[HARUKA]
Hey, Rin!
[RIN]
Go on, guys, I'll catch up.
--[NITORI] Okay.
--[CLUB MEMBERS] Yes, sir.
[RIN]
Got something on your mind?
You and me need to talk.
Meet me outside
Iwatobi High around dusk.
What's this about?
C'mon, you're not pissed 'cause
we got the same times, are ya?
[HARUKA]
Show up or don't, your choice.
Yo, it's me! Are you in there?
Let's do this. Whatever it is.
Huh.
Nothin' like chickening out
of your own show down.
[RIN]
Uh, okay...
[RIN gasps]
[NAGISA]
Take him away!
[MAKOTO and REI]
Ki-ki!
[RIN]
What the--? Put me down!
[HARUKA]
Don't be such a baby.
[NAGISA]
Haru, stay on script!
[HARUKA]
I mean, don't fight it.
[RIN] Somebody better
explain this to me!
[GOU]
Guys! What are you doing?
Put him down, now!
[RIN] Gou, is that you?
What's going on?
I'm gonna cause
some major damage
if you don't get this
stupid thing off--
[RIN gasps]
Remember that time
in elementary school
when you told me your dream?
You wanted to swim in
a pool of cherry blossoms.
Our original plan was to
spruce up the pool a little
as an advertisement
aimed at new members.
Miss A got us permission
to open it early.
But no one came, so the
work was all for naught.
[MAKOTO] Seemed like a shame to
let the end result go to waste,
so. we, uh, y'know,
thought you'd appreciate it.
This is amazing.
[RIN sobs]
[GOU chuckles]
[REI]
Well go on. Take a dip.
[RIN]
What?
Enjoy yourself!
I mean, since you're here
and all, you might as well.
Not to be ungrateful,
but it's still sorta chilly
for a swim, don't you think?
Bah, come on!
Don't be a wuss, get in there!
[REI]
It'll be bracing!
[NAGISA] Don't be afraid!
Couple minutes won't kill ya!
[RIN] Nobody's afraid!
Look, I just don't feel like--
[thunder rumbles]
[GOU yells]
[NAGISA]
Argh! It's freezing!
[NAGISA] It's not gonna
let up any time soon.
All that breathtaking beauty
spoiled by a little rainfall.
Is your glass
always half empty?
I mean, I'm just sayin'.
[REI]
I'm being a realist!
[MAKOTO] I didn't even know that
rain was in the forecast today.
[RIN]
Hey, uh.
You guys... you ever
give any thought
to life after graduation?
Not really.
So you have no idea
what you're gonna do?
Heh, heh. We can't all have
our sights set as high as you.
[RIN]
You're kidding, right?
I've wasted so much time,
it's not even funny.
The Nationals this summer are
my last shot at being scouted.
They'll be coming from all over.
I need to batten down,
focus on bringing my A-game.
[RIN]
But seriously, though.
What're you gonna do once
high school's just a memory?
Wish I could say.
Truth is, I haven't decided.
Tch.
[RIN]
How can you not have a plan?
[birds chirp]
Aw, poor tree
looks all naked.
[REI] And to add insult to
injury, the pool's a mess.
[MAKOTO]
Might as well get to cleaning.
Yeah, alright.
[bell rings]
Might have been staged,
but I dunno,
it looked pretty real to me.
[STUDENT 1B]
Hey, thanks man. I owe you one.
Yeah, sure.
[TEACHER 1A]
Take your seats, please.
I'd like to introduce
your new classmate.
Just transferred this morning.
Everyone, please join me in
welcoming one Sosuke Yamazaki.
He comes to us all
the way from Tokyo.
[applause]
Holy crap.
[SOSUKE chuckles]
[HARUKA]
Iwamoge, god of the ocean,
transforms Rin into a cyborg
and commands him to save Gou
from a ruthless band of pirates.
[REI] Um, we vetoed
the comic book idea?
[NAGISA] What's with the
new guy over at Samezuka?
Anybody know his story?
[HARUKA] Next time:
Stroke of Chance Encounter.
Where our rival team's
newest addition
will be revealed
by divine vision!
[REI] Let it go! We're done
with the sea god shtick!
[NAGISA] I thought
it was kinda cool.