[NITORI] Rin, I know we've only
roomed together for a year,
but I just wanted to say thank
you for everything you've done.
Dude, relax, what are you
gettin' so emotional about?
We're just changing rooms
'cause it's a new school year.
[NITORI sniffles]
Yeah, I suppose you're right.
I won't be around
to clean up after you,
so you'll have to deal
with your own mess.
Later.
[RIN]
One more thing...
Uh! What is it?
Just make sure you look
after this guy too, okay?
Yo! Bro!
How cool is it that
we're roomin' together?
I think it's better if I take
the top bunk, though, right?
Yeah, sure, okay.
[MOMOTARO]
All right! Yoohoo!
[NITORI] I mean, I'm glad
he joined the swim team
and everything, but the thought
of sharing a room with Momo
for a whole year makes me
a little bit sick to my stomach.
[SOSUKE]
Rin.
If I remember,
You're more of a
bottom bunk type of guy.
Yeah, but,
somethin' tells me you are too.
[RIN, SOUSUKE]
Let's go!
[RIN] Hm?
[SOSUKE] Uh?
[SOSUKE]
Iwatobi Fest?
[RIN]
Oh yeah.
Gou sent that to me actually.
The fest is today.
What, are you not gonna go?
[RIN] Ah, I don't have
time for that stuff.
[SOSUKE] Hey, you ought'a go
see her sometimes, you know?
It makes her sad when you get
all withdrawn and distant.
[door slams]
Who're you talking about?
Is it Gou?
[RIN] If I were you, I'd hurry
up and get to the pool.
[MOMOTARO]
Come on, dude, I can't breathe!
[GOU] The Iwatobi Fest
is our club's last chance
to recruit new members!
If we win the inter-club relay,
everybody is gonna
wanna join our team!
So make sure you
bring your "A-game".
Go out there and do what I know
all of you are capable of doing!
Let's race to victory and
rope in some new members,
preferably ones with
wonderful muscles
and tight, washboard abs!
[GROUP]
Yeah!
[ANNOUNCER 3A] And now it's
time for the main event!
Iwatobi's famous
inter-club relay!
Let's meet the competitors,
the Tennis, Basketball, Rugby,
Kendo, Judo and Swim Clubs.
But which will find
victory in the end?
All right, here we go!
[REFEREE 3A]
On your marks...
Get set...
[bang]
[HARUKA]
The wind is alive too.
[MAKOTO gasps]
[HARUKA] The moment
you take your first step.
It bares its fangs and
hits you with everything.
But even then, there's
nothing to worry about.
You don't fight
against the wind.
You use your fingers to make
a space and let your body
slip right on through.
Arm.
Head.
Chest.
[GOU]
Wow, perfect form.
Although...
He's so slow.
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
The Swim Club is in last place!
I'm no expert on
the subject but still.
It looks to me like
he's no good on land.
[MAKOTO]
Haru!
[HARUKA]
Makoto!
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
Amazing!
That's the smoothest
handoff I've ever seen!
Looks like the Swim Club
is really in sync!
And they're catching up
to the top of the pack!
The Basketball Club
is in the lead...
Whoa, they're in third place!
Makoto, run like your
life depends on it!
Makoto!
[MAKOTO]
Nagisa!
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
Oh no!
The Swim Club's kickboard is in
the air, but he retrieves it!
Now the Swim Club needs to
catch up again from last place!
He's doing everything he can...
Gosh, he's almost there.
If only they hadn't dropped
the darn kickboard.
Just you wait.
Huh?
[REI]
Wind speed, 1.5.
Assuming a speed
of 23 kilometers,
given Nagisa's height,
receiving a kickboard
with X amount of surface area,
if I pick the arm
with the least wind resistance,
I should be right as rain.
Left.
[NAGISA]
Go, Rei!
[ANNOUNCER 3A]
Whoa!
Now that's advanced
baton handling!
Hey, I thought the
track and field team
didn't enter this event!
It's anybody's race!
But who will it be?
Who's gonna be the victor?
Yeah!
--Go!
--Run!
[ANNOUNCER 3A] This is gonna
come down to the wire!
And the Swim Club wins the day!
[GOU, HANAMURA squeal]
No one's here!
I thought that somebody
would've shown up for sure!
Well, no matter how
strong we are at running,
at the end of the day,
we're still a Swim Club.
We did everything we
could out there you guys.
Now we just wait patiently.
Besides, you know
what happens today right?
[ALL gasp]
[MAKOTO]
They open the pool!
Let's forget the race
and the recruiting
and switch gears to the
upcoming District Tournament.
Be careful warming up.
That water is ice cold.
We have a few days before
we have to turn in our forms.
In addition to individual races,
we'll probably wanna sign up
for something else.
Huh, I wonder what
it could be...
Let me think.
[REI, GOU, NAGISA]
The medley relay!
Right, that's it.
What do ya say, Haru?
Well, I uh--
[REI, GOU, NAGISA gasp]
I only swim
freestyle and relay.
[GROUP laughs]
[MAKOTO]
Then it's decided.
We'll enter the relay.
Figure out your own individual
races before the deadline.
And you know...
Since this is my last year,
I'm thinking about
entering the freestyle
category too.
[NAGISA]
Really?
In that case, maybe I'll
try swimming butterfly!
[MAKOTO chuckles] But that's
your worst stroke, isn't it?
[NAGISA grumbles]
[MAKOTO laughs]
Yeah, but it gives me
somethin' to work on!
Hey, Rei.
Since we're branching out,
you oughta try breaststroke!
I don't wanna look stupid.
The Butterfly is still the
only stroke I can swim!
Aw.
Come on, buddy, don't beat
yourself up like that.
Besides, you're a completely
different person now, remember?
If you put your mind to it,
you can swim anything you want!
Yeah? You think so?
[GOU]
He's right.
I mean why not.
You're learning something
brand new every day!
Well.
I suppose with hard work,
anything is possible, isn't it?
Even my doing the backstroke.
If you set your mind to it,
it's more than possible.
I'm sure it'll be an
amazing thing to behold.
[REI]
In that case, I'm in!
Hm! I'll present my
backstroke, breaststroke
and freestyle to you all.
And it will be breathtaking!
[GOU, NAGISA]
Hooray!
[REI gasps]
Man, I suck!
Oh, Don't worry about it!
Hey! You didn't suck,
your form was great!
Take your time and relax.
No sense rushing it, okay?
[REI sighs]
[HARUKA]
Rei.
[REI]
Huh?
If you don't wanna
swim other strokes,
then there's no point in
forcing yourself to do it.
As long as there's
one style of swimming
that suits you. That's enough.
[REI] I can't stop thinking
about what Haru said.
But, the problem is I don't
know if I agree with him.
I'm trying as hard as I can,
but I can't even keep up
with my teammates.
If underclassmen joined
the Swim Club today.
I don't think I
could legitimately
call myself their senior.
Besides, despite what Haru says
I want to excel at
a number of things.
In the end, butterfly's
simply not enou--
--[SERA] Look who it is!
--[REI] Uh!
How've you been Ryugazaki?
[REI]
Sera, what's up?
I watched you and your team run
in the inter-club relay,
and I gotta say,
I was really impressed
with your speed.
Thanks for the compliment,
but we're a Swim Club,
so me being fleet of
foot doesn't exactly
do us much good, does it?
[SERA]
Hm.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
It sure would help the
Track and Field Club though.
Huh?
You shine on the land.
Look, I'm just sayin', if you
wanna come back and join us,
we'd love to have you.
How are you in the water anyway?
Are you any good at it?
Well. I mean, I'm new, but...
Uh--
[SERA] The offer's on the table
if you change your mind.
And I, for one, hope you do.
Cause we could use ya.
I'll see ya later.
[HARUKA sighs]
[GOU]
Hey, Haruka.
Is something
the matter with you?
[HARUKA]
Can I ask you something?
[GOU]
Hm?
I heard a college scout
came at Sosuke
with a full court press.
But, he decided he wanted
to swim at home during his
last year in high school,
so I guess that's why he
transferred to Samezuka.
If you know what's
good for you,
you'll stay out of Rin's way.
So what's up? Did something
happen with Sosuke?
Doesn't matter.
You'll get scouted too!
Especially if you do well
in the tournament!
It's a big opportunity
to show your stuff!
[HARUKA]
I swim for myself.
No one else.
[water splashes]
[NAGISA]
Oh!
The water's so warm!
[MAKOTO]
Especially compared to the pool.
It's freezing in there.
[REI]
He swims for himself.
Not for anybody else.
Who do I swim for?
[NAGISA] And then, Haru's eyes
went all sparkly like, huzzah!
[MAKOTO chuckles]
Hey! Rei! What do
you say we head over
to Haru's house and
hang out for a little while?
Sorry, but I can't.
I mean, I really wish I could
and all, but I've already
made plans tonight, so I'll
have to take a rain-check.
Is he okay?
[TEACHER 3A] Along those lines,
there is a profound connection
between the book
and current times.
If you look at the modern
parallels the underlying
question should become crystal
clear. So what's the question?
[NAGISA]
Well, Ryugazaki?
[REI]
Yes!
[TEACHER 3A] Young man, do you
need to go to the bathroom?
Huh? Oh. No. Please! I'm fine!
[STUDENTS laugh]
[REI]
I can't believe I fell asleep
and freaked out like that!
But I'm not a lunatic,
I swear I heard a voice.
[NAGISA]
Oh. Forget that.
After class, do you
wanna come hang out?
Uh--
I'm sorry, but I already have
plans today too, so I can't.
What? Not again...
There's a new fro-yo place
in front of the station
if you wanna come with.
I wish I could.
But I've got stuff today.
Hey, I was thinkin'
we could hang out
at your place after school.
I'm so sorry.
But I can't today either.
So, Rei, what are
you doing after this?
[REI]
Sorry, I gotta run.
I made plans already,
maybe next time!
[TEACHER 3A]
As you can see, there are many
different meanings hidden in the
text, but the real question is.
Where to look?
[NAGISA] Something weird
is going on with Rei!
I think you're overreacting.
Yeah, it's not like he's
missed any practices.
Well, maybe not.
But last Sunday, I dropped by
his house unannounced
just to check in on him.
And when I did...
...he wasn't even home.
His mom answered the door.
He always studies at home
on Sundays, so where was he?
Hey, now that you mention it,
I saw him last Sunday.
--You did?
--[GOU] Yeah.
[GOU] My friend Hana and I went
to the grocery store together
to get some cooking stuff.
[GOU]
And there he was.
I would've said "hi" but he
seemed busy with the deserts.
[SASABE]
I know what's wrong.
He's got a sickness.
[GROUP]
Huh?
Yeah. He's sick in love!
[GOU, MAKOTO]
Love?
Yep, I'd say your buddy Rei's
probably got himself
a girlfriend.
Do you think so?
Oh my goodness!
There are two types
of men in this world.
Those who get stronger when
pricked by cupid's arrow
and those who get weaker.
Was that an impression
of Miss Amakata?
[GOU] If what he said
is true, Rei is definitely
the type who gets weaker.
Ah! This is bad. Real bad!
What's the big deal?
[MAKOTO] Hm... Well, he could
become so wrapped up
with his new lady friend that
he neglects the Swim Club.
No!
I wouldn't worry.
I got this. Leave it to me!
[REI]
So what's this about?
[GOU]
Well, Rei.
You can talk to me
about what's going on
with you, you know?
Whatever's happening,
you don't have to face it alone!
[REI]
Thank you? But...
Nothing's "going on" with me.
[REI laughs]
Enamored?
That's the most ridiculous
thing that I've ever heard!
Huh? So you're not in love?
Of course not!
You really think I'd be
dumb enough to fall prey
to something so preposterously
illogical as love?
Then why were you looking
at cakes the other day?
Uh. Because I suddenly felt like
eating some cake,
what's wrong with that?
Just tell me the truth. Where
have you been disappearing to?
[REI] Nowhere, I've just
been busy, that's all.
Busy with what exactly?
Just stuff, you know,
stuff that, when I do it,
keeps me busy. It's not like
I'm breaking any ethical code
withholding my whereabouts!
Uh! Speaking of which, I have
something today that's liable
to keep me very occupied
indeed, so, goodbye!
Yeah. You're right.
He's bein' weird.
So sweet...
[knocking]
[MOMOTARO]
Hey Rin, sorry to bother you.
But would you be willing to take
a look at my training regimen
for tomorrow morning? Ah!
Cleavage? Whoa...
Hey.
Uh! I can come back!
[RIN]
No, just get on with it.
[MOMOTARO]
Wait, uh!
So. Are those, like, some
homemade cookies or somethin'?
Why, do you want one?
[MOMOTARO]
Uh! Oh yeah!
Yahoo!
[MOMOTARO]
Oh man, that is so good!
Can I have another one?
Didn't you hear me?
I said "one."
[MOMOTARO]
Stingy!
[SERA]
Oh! What's up, Rei?
[REI]
Not much.
Look, about our little
discussion the other day...
Who is that?
He has beautiful
brachioradialis muscles!
Oh no! I didn't mean that!
Could it be...?
[GOU]
I'm telling you, I saw them!
[MAKOTO]
So, what happened?
[NAGISA]
Come on!
[GOU]
Well. It was--
I don't know
how to say this.
But the truth is...
I think he might've
been Rei's boyfriend!
[MAKOTO, NAGISA]
What?
[NAGISA]
No way!
Guys.
We're jumping to conclusions,
they're probably just friends.
Hey, I know who
you're talking about.
[GOU] That's him, with the
brachioradialis muscles!
Hold on.
Isn't he the
track and field captain?
You really think Rei
and this guy might be--?
Or maybe after
running in the relay,
Rei decided he missed
track and field.
Wait, you think he's
considering going back?
Makoto!
Are you saying he's going
to quit the Swim Club?
No way! He can't
do that! It's not fair!
Yeah, you're right.
[NAGISA]
Huh?
Don't worry, I'm not
gonna let that happen.
[REI]
I'm sorry I'm running late.
Hey, what's going on?
Oh, nothing's going on.
Nothing at all.
We're just wondering if
you're "occupied" again?
Um-- I might be.
[MAKOTO]
In that case...
Club's cancelled today.
I call an emergency meeting
at Haru's house!
[GOU, NAGISA]
Yeah!
Hip. Hip. Hooray!
[REI]
So, uh...
Does someone wanna tell me
what this meeting's all about?
Let's see. Uh. Well...
I guess it slipped my mind?
Hey, don't look at me.
It's about uh...
Oh, I remember!
It's about a tasting
for new mackerel recipes.
Oh, come on, does that
sound like an emergency to you?
[HARUKA] This was your
genius plan, you go for it.
[MAKOTO whispering]
No. You go.
[REI]
If there's nothing pressing,
I have somewhere to be,
if you'll be kind enough
to excuse me...
--[MAKOTO] No, please! Wait!
--[NAGISA, GOU yelp]
[NAGISA]
Don't go!
[REI]
What is wrong with you?
[NAGISA] Whatever you do,
don't quit the Swim Club!
Huh?
[NAGISA] We know what
you've been up to.
Don't deny it.
You're leaving us for the Track
and Field Club, aren't you?
It's not fair!
You can't leave!
But, Nagisa--
[MAKOTO]
He's right, Rei.
We're not just gonna
let you quit like this.
What kind of teammates
would that make us?
As your manager,
I'm afraid that I can't accept
you leaving either, Rei.
Listen, Rin and I were
saved because of you.
After everything,
you're just gonna quit now?
I'm not gonna
stand for it. Period.
[HARUKA]
Besides, man.
You're the one who wanted the
four of us to go to Nationals!
I did say that, didn't I?
[NAGISA]
You promised!
Do you remember what you said?
You swore we would all four
swim a relay together!
You gave us your word
that you'd show us
a beautiful butterfly
stroke at Nationals!
You can't abandon us now!
[REI]
You guys are sweet.
But I don't know what
you're talking about.
Rest assured, if you
think I'm gonna quit,
you're barking up
the wrong tree.
But you were with the captain
of the Track and Field Club.
Wait a sec, you saw us?
He did ask me to come back,
but that's all it was, I swear.
Trust me on this, guys.
It's nothing.
This club is
too important to me.
I am in this for the long haul!
[GROUP sighing, laughing]
Now that we've resolved
that misunderstanding,
I've got somewhere I need to be,
so I'd better get going.
See ya later!
[NAGISA whispering]
He leaves us no choice.
We've gotta follow him.
[MAKOTO]
Are we where I think we are?
Guys, this is Samezuka Academy.
[RIN]
That's it. Looks good.
Use your hips as a center
to find your balance.
Don't forget to paddle
at the same time you exhale.
And remember to do the thing
I taught you earlier, okay?
[RIN]
Ready?
Yeah!
[REI coughing]
Good job, man, you did it!
I really did, didn't I?
Yeah!
Well, let's do the breaststroke
next, what do ya say?
Heck yeah!
I really gotta hand it
to you, buddy,
you've done a good job
learning how to swim.
You wanna hear the truth?
I didn't expect you'd
make it this far.
I've been thinking about
this for a while now...
I thought I could be like Haru.
Be content with mastering the
butterfly and nothing else.
There was definitely no
beauty in me flailing around.
And I thought, "if that's
really the best I can do,
why even bother?
I'd rather just quit."
However, I am no quitter.
How could I live with myself
if I gave up that easily?
[RIN]
Hm?
[REI] I'm sorry for making
you help me everyday,
I'm sure it gets on your nerves.
[RIN] If it's after practice,
I don't mind.
Besides...
All things considered,
I think I owe you.
[REI]
What?
[RIN]
Ah, forget about it.
Are we here to talk or work?
If you want those guys
to be surprised
then you have a long way to go.
[REI]
Right!
Oh, wow...
So the reason Rei's doing this
is 'cause he wants
to surprise us?
Yep.
[NAGISA]
Guys!
Can you believe it, Rei's
swimming the breaststroke?
[GROUP gasps]
[MAKOTO]
Awesome!
[NAGISA]
He did the turn too!
[MAKOTO]
This is unbelievable!
[GOU] You guys,
he's swimming this way!
[NAGISA]
Crap!
[door creaks]
[RIN sighs]
[SOSUKE] I can't believe
you're doing this every day.
Shut up.
[RIN] We're on different teams,
but we're still friends.
Besides, seeing him leave
it all out there like that...
Makes me want to train harder
and give everything
I've got, too.
'Cause you're doing
it all for them... Right?
[RIN]
Anyway, today was the last day.
Looks like he's gotten
the hang of it.
He should be fine.
No joke. That guy
worked his tail off. Wow.
Well, I'm glad, Rin.
[NITORI]
Hey. What's that?
Oh, these are Gou's
famous homemade cookies.
I asked Rin if I could
please have another,
and he told me that
I could help myself!
Uh, I'm sorry to
burst your bubble,
but Gou didn't
make those. Rei did.
Ah!
[NITORI] Apparently, he was
gonna go with making
Rin a cake at first.
Y'know, as a way to say
"thanks for all the help,"
but when he thought about
Rin's physical condition,
he figured it'd be better
to bake him, like,
health-food cookies.
[REI]
Thanks for waiting, everyone!
Get ready!
Because the time to reveal my
new form has arrived at last!
[REI chuckles]
Try not to be too surprised.
And away we go!
[water splashes]
Look, Rei is swimming freestyle.
It's so amazing!.
He really did learn
all the strokes!
Can you guys believe it?
You're not acting
surprised enough.
Why can't you try to put
a little more into it!
Wow! Holy Mackerel!
Yeah, how did he learn
to swim like that?
I'm truly flabbergasted
beyond words!
You three really are
hopeless, aren't you?
You know, I think it's better
if we just tell him the truth.
[MAKOTO] Have you completely
lost your mind?
All right. Guys. So.
Wh-Wha-What'd you
think of my swimming?
You're shocked, aren't you?
You'd have never seen this
coming in a million years!
[HARUKA] Rei. You worked
really hard, huh?
I did!
[NAGISA] Hey, I wanna try
your cookies too, Rei!
[REI] I've got a special
surprise for you:
a cookie with the
vitamin C of 30 lemons
crammed into one
delicious treat!
[NAGISA]
So, a sour cookie?
[REI] If you convert the vitamin
C of 30 lemons to mackerel,
you'll get 50 mackerels worth.
[NAGISA]
All right!
[REI] I wonder what mackerel
cookies would taste like...
[HARUKA] Next time:
"Somersault Turn of Promise"
[REI]
What I wanna know is:
what happened in
Rin and Sosuke's past?