[MAKOTO]
Haru!
Rin!
[RIN]
Hey, Makoto!
Long way to come just to
see us get off the plane.
Bet you guys are pretty
wiped out from the trip.
Uh... I-I...
[MAKOTO]
Haru.
Huh?
It's good to see you.
Good to see you, too.
So, uh. What do you
say we get goin'?
So, ya think we're finally
getting our heads around
this pool, or what?
Yeah. And just imagine
two days from now
when these stands'll be
filled with spectators!
Sounds like someone's
gettin' nervous.
Oh, please.
No, it just happens to be a day
we've all worked very hard for.
I am as far from nervous
as it's possible to be!
So you've finally grown
some hair on your chest!
Why do you--?
Makoto will be back with
them any minute now!
Whoa. Guess we
lost track of time.
C'mon, man.
I can't help but wonder.
Do you really think the trip
had a positive effect on Haru?
[NAGISA]
Sure it did!
He just needed a little
change of scenery, that's all.
You'll see!
[REI]
Right!
[MAKOTO]
Guys are here.
Thought it'd be good to
get to know the space.
You know, since
tomorrow's the big day.
Well, I'm gonna go
meet up with my team, so,
see ya.
[HARUKA]
Rin!
Thanks a lot, man.
No worries.
[MAKOTO]
Hey!
[REI, NAGISA]
Hm?
[NAGISA]
Haru!
[REI]
Welcome back!
[HARUKA]
Hi, Rei. Nagisa.
Hope the trip was cool!
Glad you made it home!
And more importantly,
that you made it home safe.
[NAGISA]
You are such a mother-hen, Rei.
He was super stressed out
about you the whole time.
[REI]
Shut up!
I'm sorry I made you guys
worry about me.
No biggie.
Just do us all a favor and
get plenty of rest before
the big tournament,
it is only two days away.
Of course, we still need to
make a few minor adjustments.
[NAGISA]
That's true.
[HARUKA]
Makoto.
Nagisa, Rei. We need to talk.
It's important.
[HARUKA] 'Til now, I was
never really concerned
about winning or
losing, you know?
I just swam 'cause I wanted to.
I thought if I made it
about tweaking my speed,
or beating the other team or
whatever, what'd be the point?
Rin wants to swim at the
international level.
He's diving into that world
head-first after we graduate.
But, that's his thing.
Should I follow his
example if I just wanna
keep swimming,
or is that a compromise?
Is it for me to
care about winning?
I don't think so. I'm not Rin.
I don't have the
competitive streak he does.
[HARUKA]
So, that's why I couldn't answer
when you asked what my plan was.
I didn't have a clue.
Didn't think a dream was
something you could just grab.
But then, Rin took
me to Australia,
showed me all this
amazing stuff.
And suddenly it
was like-- I dunno.
[RIN] What makes a dream
really and truly yours?
[HARUKA] I felt it, like the
world got a lot bigger.
And me? I'd found
my place in it.
I wanna swim for
the rest of my life.
And if that means I gotta
start caring about times
and tournaments and all the
things that come with it.
That's fine with me.
Wow, that's quite a change
of heart for you, dude.
Sounds like the trip with
Rin was a real eye opener.
I knew it was gonna work out!
If you've found your path,
then far be it from us
to give you anything
but support.
You better believe we'll be
cheering you on all the way!
I know you will.
Thanks.
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Good morning!
[RIN]
Hey.
Hope you had a good trip
there and back, Captain!
It was awesome.
Been any earth-shattering
changes since I left?
No, sir-- I mean, Rin--
we've been--
What'd you get me?
Can I have my
souvenir now?
Subtle. Nice.
Why not? Sure.
Knock yourself out.
Awesome! It's a boomerang!
[RIN, NITORI laugh]
[UOZUMI]
Dude, that's perfect for you.
[MOMOTARO]
G'day, mate!
Hey is Sosuke around?
[NITORI] He said he'll
catch up with us after a while.
[MAKOTO]
We're here. Do you believe it?
It still feels like a dream.
Makoto, I--
[HARUKA] The other day, I said
some really stupid things.
I didn't mean any of 'em.
I'm sorry.
Haru...
If anybody's sorry, it's me.
We've been through a lot.
I oughta be able
to talk to my friend.
Seriously.
I should've told you what
my plans were before I did.
Truth is, competition isn't my
thing. I'd been thinking about
just fallin' back
on community college
or something. Didn't know
how to bring it up.
Sucks when you don't know
what you wanna
do with your life.
Then, Coach Sasabe
gave me that job
coaching little
kids at the club.
It was nothing special at first,
just 'em helping
him out and stuff.
I figured it was the least I
could do to repay him, ya know?
But then the kids
changed all of that.
I met Hayato,
and for some reason
I really wanted to
help him learn to swim.
I was clueless at first.
But your advice actually made
more difference than you think.
[HARUKA]
Not like it was that profound.
[MAKOTO chuckles]
[MAKOTO] Well, the kid learned
how to do the backstroke.
And the look on his
face when he did;
I'd never seen anything
like it before in my life.
He was so proud of himself.
From that moment I was hooked.
That's when I knew I
wanted to help kids feel
a sense of accomplishment,
take pride in themselves.
[MAKOTO]
I was put on this Earth
to bring first-timers
to the water.
After graduation,
I'm gonna go to college
in Tokyo to make it happen.
That's my dream.
That's what I'm reaching for.
Not bad.
You do realize you're gonna
be awesome at it, right?
You really think so?
Thanks, man.
It'll be the hardest
thing I've ever done.
[HARUKA]
No kidding.
[MAKOTO laughs]
[MOMOTARO gasps]
[SOSUKE] Give yourself
more time to recover.
Your center of balance is off.
[MOMOTARO]
Sosuke!
Oh, hey.
Sorry I'm late. Got here
as soon as I could.
So, Australia. Good?
Oh, yeah, it's incredible.
[SOSUKE]
Man.
Kind of a long way
to go to make a point.
Yeah, well. It's worth it.
And I'd do it all again
in a heartbeat.
[NAGISA laughs]
Bet you would.
[AMAKATA]
Alright, boys! Special occasion.
Tomorrow's the big day.
So pick anything on the menu.
My treat.
[BOYS]
Whoa!
Wow, that's incredibly
generous of you!
Alrighty, then! Seafood salad,
garlic potato salad,
beer-battered fish n' chips,
roast beef,
french onion soup,
Yorkshire pudding,
chicken alfredo,
pasta pescatore, unagi,
sweet potato fries
with truffle oil,
three cheese omelet,
porcini cream risotto,
lobster mac n' cheese,
oysters on the half shell,
swordfish--
[AMAKATA]
Okay, okay!
Mac n' cheese sounds absolutely
delicious, let's do that.
But what do you say we
try it without the lobster?
[NAGISA]
But!
Easy, she is doing this
on a teacher's salary.
They have mackerel here?
Uh, I don't think
they're that sort
of place, dude.
[REI] Hmm. They have
mackerel meuniere.
[HARUKA]
Not salt-grilled?
Is it just me or is there
something different
about Haru?
Not that it's any of my
business, but I'd noticed
the gang being a little
short with each other lately.
I think the trip to
Australia with my brother
did him a lot of good.
[AMAKATA]
I should say so.
[HARUKA]
Why don't they have sashimi?
[REI]
Sashimi?
He seems in a better place.
I'm glad.
[NAGISA]
What a meal!
I'm surprised you can still move
with all the food
you packed away.
Ah, I'm good.
I'm still growin',
so I gotta eat!
We believe you.
Oh, honestly.
With how you put it away, you'll
sink straight to the bottom.
We don't need you cramping
up at the tournament.
[NAGISA]
Whoa! It's so beautiful!
[REI]
Yes it is.
[MAKOTO] The ocean looks
completely different here.
Tomorrow really is the day.
[MAKOTO]
Gives you chills, doesn't it?
I mean, when you think back
to when this all started.
None of us ever imagined
that we'd make it this far.
We couldn't even use
our own pool at first.
[NAGISA]
That's right.
The whole thing started
with us fixing it up.
Haru was obsessed.
He'd have done anything to swim.
[NAGISA giggles] Oh, man!
Remember at the hardware store?
You started stripping
down to your skivvies
in front of the fish tanks.
[REI]
Ugh. Glad I wasn't there.
[MAKOTO laughs]
Yeah, you weren't with us yet,
were you, Rei? I forgot
that was before your time.
You'd originally gone
with the track team,
isn't that right?
Indeed.
Your little Swim Club made
absolutely no sense to me.
But then, Nagisa asked
me to join.
And seeing Haru swim,
I couldn't resist.
Of course, I couldn't
hold my own with any of you,
remember that?
At training camp,
Makoto had to rescue me.
[REI]
I shudder to think
what I would have
become without you all.
Relay swimming isn't just fun,
it's become a way life.
It helped me find
who I really am.
Aw.
This wouldn't have been
possible without Nagisa.
It was his idea
to start the club.
Okay, come on, you gotta stop.
I'm gonna blush.
None of us would
be here without you,
you know that, right?
And look at you now.
Not that long ago
you were a runaway.
[REI] And yet, here you are,
grade point average soaring,
and the club you founded making
it all the way to Nationals.
Look at yourself.
I mean, Rei,
you had a rough start.
In the early days,
you swam like a boat anchor.
And now, your butterfly
stroke is untouchable!
Even when your goggles
came off that one time!
[REI] That was a decidedly
less than beautiful moment.
[NAGISA]
Whatever! It was fantastic!
[MAKOTO] You hit your stride
with butterfly and now,
there's not a stroke you
can't do. You should be proud.
Well, yes.
But without Rin's help, I would
never would've dreamed of-- Uh--
[NAGISA]
Dude. We've known for a while.
[REI]
Really?
Sorry, Rei. We know
you were trying to
keep that whole
night lesson thing secret.
Uh... You might've
said something
and spared me the embarrassment.
I don't think the man
will ever know how
enormously grateful I am.
Well, man, you aren't
the only one who owes him.
I'd lost my way for a bit
when Rin showed up again.
Only thing I cared about was me.
But, Rin brought me out of
the funk I'd put myself in,
made me realize
how you guys felt.
What it really meant
to swim as a team.
Things were so
different back then.
That first relay with all of you
really opened my eyes, no joke.
Remember how nervous we were?
It was hard enough just
learning how to swim together.
But it wasn't too long before
we started competing
in actual tournaments.
Man, we had so much fun
that first time out, right?
Oh, yes.
Except of course
losing to Samezuka
proved to be a rather
bitter pill to swallow.
Ah yeah.
You seriously lit a fire
under us after that, Rei.
So we started practicing
our exchanges for Regionals.
Talk about hard work payin' off
when push came to shove! Hey!
We keep doing like we're doing,
next year Regionals
won't know what hit 'em!
We'll kill it at training camp,
set new records--
The four of us are
unbeatable! Am I right?
Well, except it won't
be the four of us then.
Tomorrow's the last race
these two will swim
before they graduate.
Oh... Oh, yeah.
Things will be different.
Daily practice, training camp,
the tournaments, all of it.
Who knows when the four of us
might swim together, again?
Ever...
Dude, are you--?
[REI]
Oh. How awkward.
Rei, come on...
No. Screw this. This sucks!
Why can't things
stay the way they are?
We've been through so much!
We've come so far!
I want us to swim
together forever!
I do, too! I can't do this!
I learned to swim for us,
what do I do now?
I'm not ready
for this to be over.
[NAGISA whimpering, sobbing]
[REI, NAGISA sobbing]
Come on, you two.
No more tears.
Be strong. You can
do that, right?
[NAGISA sobs]
I'm sorry.
Hey, it's okay.
There's no reason
to get all choked up.
We're swimming a
race tomorrow, aren't we?
We're still a team
for one more day.
Yes, but...
[HARUKA]
He's right.
[NAGISA]
Haru...
[HARUKA] Whatever happens,
we'll always have that.
Whatever life throws at us,
wherever our paths lead,
we'll be connected by
what we've been through.
Connected by the water.
[HARUKA]
This isn't the end for us.
Just a little change of scenery.
Very beautifully said.
We'll always be a team?
[MAKOTO]
Mm-hm.
[MAKOTO] I feel like we're
gonna see something today
that'll stay with us forever.
[HARUKA]
Definitely. All four of us.
[REI]
Agreed.
[NAGISA]
Let's do this!
[CROWD cheers]
[MAKOTO, REI, NAGISA]
Whoa...
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 13A]
The first heat of the
men's four-hundred-meter
medley relay begins now.
Swimmers, on your marks.
[SASABE]
Makoto!
[GIRLS]
[MALE REFEREE 13A]
Ready...
[beep]
[CROWD]
Go!
It's exactly like I remember it.
[MAKOTO laughs]
Nagisa!
[NAGISA giggles]
It's all you!
[REI laughs]
Bring it home, Haruka!
[MAKOTO]
Haru.
[NAGISA]
Nice job.
[REI]
Beautifully done.
--[MAKOTO] Come on!
--[REI] You can do it!
[HARUKA gasps]
[CROWD cheers]
[GOU]
He did it! He did it!
Heh.
[NAGISA sobs]
[NAGISA, REI sobbing]
[REI sobbing]
[MAKOTO laughs]
[HARUKA laughs]
[MAKOTO]
Yeah!
[RIN gasps]
[RIN]
What's the matter, ladies?
No one got the grapes
to take on the captain?
Momo?
[MOMOTARO] Give me a
second to not die, will ya?
[RIN] Today, we third
years say good-bye.
Lot of change on the horizon.
Come April,
there'll be new recruits.
The club, as you know,
it'll be overhauled.
My hope for each and every
one of you is that you'll
make the cut, be part
of the Regionals team.
The year after that, same thing:
new recruits, new team.
I want you to feel like
you're carrying the torch,
keeping the dream alive
from season to season.
You all need to know
that you're part
of something bigger
than yourselves!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Yes, sir!
Heh. Nice. Surprised
you're not bawling.
[NITORI whimpering]
[RIN] Ai!
Sir!
Next year, you call the shots.
I'm making you captain.
Sir!
[MOMOTARO]
Go Nitori!
[UOZUMI]
Congratulations, Captain!
[SOSUKE]
Rin?
[RIN]
Where you getting this idea
that your shoulder
can't be fixed?
[SOSUKE]
What?
Are you seriously
out of the game?
Or are you closing the
door on your dreams
before you even try?
Give it some thought.
When you decide not to
be done, I'll be waiting.
[SOSUKE]
Wow. 'Course you'd say that.
What else did I expect?
Well, it hasn't
fallen on deaf ears.
Ugh. I don't like this.
When's big brother coming back?
Uh, hey. Don't be a baby.
He's busy, Tokyo's a
big place and he's got
lots of hard studyings to do.
He'll be back.
When he's finished.
Crap, I'm gonna miss
my stupid train!
[doorbell rings]
[MAKOTO sighs]
He's never gonna learn.
It's me, dude. I'm comin' in.
Are you decent?
[HARUKA gasps]
[MAKOTO]
C'mon, man.
We miss our flight, it's gonna
be a pain in the butt to rebook.
Haruka.
Ugh. Why you gotta
say my name like that?
It sounds weird.
[MAKOTO] Hey, guys!
I know, we suck. Sorry.
[REI]
Well, shall we be on our way?
Hey guys, do me a favor.
Before we go to Rin's,
there's some place
I'd like to stop first.
[SASABE]
Huh? What's this supposed to be?
[MAKOTO]
Ah.
We wrote down all the stuff
we saw when we swam.
Figured we'd commit
to posterity.
What a cool idea!
Mind if I have a looksee?
With all due respect,
this is a time capsule.
The point is to keep it
sealed 'til we open it up
years from now and
fondly reminisce.
For now, they're strictly
classified. Sorry.
[RIN]
We've been expecting you.
Step right up and feast your
eyes on an awe-inspiring sight.
Your pool!
[HARUKA gasps]
[GROUP]
Whoa!
[ALL laughing]
[ALL]
Yeah!
[CROWD cheering]
Heh.
[HARUKA]
Hmph.
[MALE REFEREE 13B]
On your marks...
[beep]
[CROWD cheers]