[JULI] I've been with you
from the very beginning.
[LOUIS] I'm glad we can see
each other whenever we want.
[JULI] No matter what.
I'll keep on protecting you.
[LOUIS] It's complicated.
But you don't have to worry.
[JULI, LOUIS]
Because we love you.
Of course we do, after all,
we're the Coalition
to Protect Chii.
[EMA]
Adopted daughter. It can't be.
[EMA] I can't believe it.
He was never really my father?
Oh, Dad.
[phone rings]
[NATSUME] Come on.
You couldn't at least answer me?
[EMA] Natsume, what
are you doing here?
[NATSUME] Um, I'm pretty
sure that's my line.
I got a call from
the guys that you
hadn't come home, so I've been
looking everywhere for you.
Really? Why?
[gasps] What do
you mean "why"?
[EMA] I don't know. Guess I'm
not worth the trouble.
[NATSUME]
Where's that coming from?
Come on, you gotta
tell me what happened.
Alright. I'll just let
Ukyo know you're safe.
[gasps] Please don't call him.
[EMA] I don't wanna go home.
I'm not ready just yet.
[NATSUME] Seriously,
you really won't tell me
what's goin' on?
Okay, you don't wanna
go home. I get it.
[sighs] Fine.
Then, would my
apartment work for you?
[gasps]
We won't have to walk too far.
It'll be better than out here.
Hope it's not too
much of a wreck.
[CAT meows]
[EMA gasps]
Tsubaki. Can you just give
me a minute to get inside!
Azusa, stop encouraging him!
Those are really their names?
Yeah.
Why I chose them is
kind of a long story.
I'll fill ya in sometime.
Well, come on in.
Make yourself at home.
[EMA]
Thank you very much.
[NATSUME]
You hungry at all?
[EMA]
Not really.
[TSUBAKI CAT purrs]
[NATSUME]
Want somethin' to drink?
[EMA]
No, I'm fine.
[NATSUME]
Well, at least go take a shower.
That always makes me feel
better when I'm upset.
[door clicks]
[EMA] Thanks again. I'm
sorry for imposing on you.
[NATSUME]
Nah, never mind that.
You ready to talk?
You don't have to tell me
if you don't want.
But, if you need my help,
I'm right here.
I appreciate that.
It's really sweet.
I just don't think I'm worth
the trouble, though.
[NATSUME] You said the
same thing earlier, too.
Why would you think that?
[EMA]
Because as soon as I got here,
everyone started fighting, and,
and then there's just
some other stuff.
[NATSUME]
Well, brothers tend to fight.
It's hard to imagine any
way that'd be your fault.
No.
But if I hadn't become a part
of the Asahina family...
[NATSUME] I'm sorry.
And I mean for all of us.
I apologize.
I had no idea things were
bothering you that much.
But, still.
Nothing we did should
have made you feel
like you're not
worth the trouble.
[EMA]
It's not just you.
[EMA] Look. It's a copy
of my family register.
[NATSUME]
Adopted?
[EMA]
That's right.
The man I thought was
my real dad, isn't.
I keep thinking,
my parents must've thought
I wasn't worth the trouble.
That had to be why they
decided to give me away.
No, there's no way that's true.
[EMA]
Why else would my dad
never say anything
to me about this?
Even worse, ever since
he married your mother,
I dunno why, but he hasn't
come to see me at all.
So it's him, too.
I'm not even worth the
trouble to my own father.
I'm sorry. I can go home.
I don't wanna
bother anyone else.
I'll just see my way out.
[NATSUME]
Hold on.
[EMA gasps]
[NATSUME]
You're wrong, you know.
All of us are lucky
to be around you.
Stay here. You don't
have to go home.
I can sleep on the floor.
And, just to make myself clear.
The truth of the matter?
Is that the Asahina
family needs you.
More than you seem to realize.
Everyone's having these
conflicts because
they all care so much about you.
Believe me, they won't
act like idiots forever.
Things'll calm down.
especially considering
what's happened tonight.
No one wants to hurt you.
Have faith in us.
I know it's hard.
But please, try.
[NATSUME]
Are you angry?
[gasps]
About me kissing you, I mean?
[EMA]
No.
I need to be honest with you.
I wouldn't have kissed
you for no reason.
I care about you.
I know saying this isn't fair.
and it'll most likely only
complicate things further.
But I can't, I can't keep
from telling you how I feel.
In the end I'm no
different from my brothers.
Because it turns out that
I'm crazy about you, too.
No, I'm sorry.
I don't wanna kiss you
like this. It's not fair.
I'll leave you alone and
let you get some sleep.
[AZUSA CAT yawns]
[door clicks]
[NATSUME]
Hey, what're you doing?
Good morni--
[gasps]
[NATSUME]
Sorry about that.
I had plenty of time before
I had to make it in to work.
So I decided to go for
a quick run, first.
[EMA]
Do you go running every morning?
[NATSUME] Yeah, for the
most part, I guess.
I kinda feel like
I owe it to Subaru.
[EMA]
To Subaru?
Never mind, forget
I mentioned it.
Anyway, it was nice of you
to cook breakfast for us.
Yeah, well.
I had to use up all the
food in the fridge.
I hope that was okay.
[NATSUME]
No prob.
[EMA]
Good.
Then, would you rather
have an omelet
or some scrambled eggs?
It's your choice.
Omelet sounds good.
An omelet it is.
[NATSUME]
You mean to tell me those jerks
get to eat stuff
like this every day?
Now I'm kinda jealous. Man.
[EMA] I didn't make
anything all that special.
They're just eggs.
Oh, now hey, come on.
You made all this yourself
in no time at all.
To me, that makes it
the best breakfast ever.
You feelin' better, today?
[EMA] Yes, I'm not all
mixed up like I was yesterday.
I'm really sorry about that.
You don't have to apologize.
Remember, you can
always talk to me.
I'll be here if
you ever need to.
Thank you. That means a lot.
[NATSUME]
Ah! No! Tsubaki! Azusa!
Man. They are so pissy!
[EMA giggles]
Ah. Nice, there it is.
[doorbell rings]
[BOTH gasp]
[LOUIS]
Um, Chii?
Hey, Louis.
[JULI]
Chii! Chii!
[NATSUME] I'm gonna let
him in. Do you mind?
They know.
Sorry, I called last night
after you got in the shower.
I had to at least tell
them you were here.
Otherwise, someone probably
would have called the police.
Definitely would have
called the police.
That's how worked up
they all were.
[EMA] I didn't know everyone
would be so worried about me.
Well hello there.
I'm sorry, you guys. I really
didn't mean to worry you.
Oh, we know you didn't mean to.
It's no problem.
And please, no need
to apologize.
You're safe, so we're happy.
Thank you, Louis.
And you, Juli. Forgive me?
There's nothing to forgive.
But you, you bastard!
How dare you kidnap
Chii like this?
[EMA]
No! Juli!
[LOUIS]
Juli, stop it.
[JULI] I can't let him
get away with this!
No, Juli. Natsume's good.
He helped. He kept Chii
safe. Isn't that right?
That's right! Juli, you
have to believe me.
Natsume helped me. That's all.
[JULI]
Be quiet, Chii.
I'm trying to punish this
disgusting creature!
Delicious, again.
Thank you for making
that, Chii. It was yummy.
[EMA]
You're welcome.
So anyway, what's the deal
with this "Chii" thing?
I don't know what you mean.
Oh, it's just a silly nickname.
[NATSUME]
Huh.
Oh! Whoops! I almost forgot!
What do you think? I'd love
it if you would try it on!
[EMA]
Huh?
If you want, I'll style
your hair, too.
Wait. Don't you
need to be getting
back to the condo sometime soon?
Not necessarily.
Besides, this'll
make her feel better.
You may be right. Fine.
I'll head over to
the condo, then.
I can let everyone
know what's goin' on.
You okay with a
little pampering?
I'm good with that.
Thanks, Louis.
I really appreciate it.
It's my pleasure.
Leave it to me.
[JULI]
Ooh, that looks cute, Chii.
[LOUIS]
Mh-mm. This works on you.
Thank you, Louis. I love it.
It's funny, I feel a million
times better already.
It's about all I
can do, right now,
but I promise you this.
I'm here, and I'll
do whatever I can.
If you need me, all you
have to do is ask.
Thank you.
Hey, me too!
Louis and I have formed
the Coalition to Protect Chii,
so that's our job.
So tell us. About yesterday,
what in the world
could have upset you that much?
[EMA] I know this must be
a shock to you, too, Juli.
Who would've thought
I wasn't actually
related to Dad, right?
Yeah... Um.
You know what, why don't
we go to the park?
Huh?
A boat ride. Sound fun?
It's nice.
[LOUIS]
Isn't it? I'm sorry.
I've just been wanting
to do this forever.
About what you said.
I understand how you feel, Chii.
More than you know.
[EMA]
Hm?
I was adopted.
This family of ours, I'm not
really related to them.
[EMA]
What?
[LOUIS] Does that come
as a surprise to you?
I get it. You'd never know.
But, I used to live
in an orphanage.
When I was two, Miss Miwa was
kind enough to take me in.
I owe everything to her.
By the time I joined the family,
they had seven boys already.
The ones up through
Natsume know I was adopted,
but the five from Subaru
on down weren't born yet.
They still haven't
been told the truth.
As a kid, there was
a period of time
that was really
difficult for me.
I was surrounded by
all these brothers
who were actually related,
and I felt like I didn't belong,
but Mom always treated me
like one of her boys.
I was her son. Strangely,
I think that made me
more conscious of it.
Of the fact that I was adopted.
And when you start accepting
that you're different,
you start noticing what
makes you that way.
Like they shared quirks.
It was so crazy.
But there I was. My quirks
weren't like theirs.
I wasn't one of them.
I wasn't a real brother.
I wasn't family. It was so hard.
I felt like, since I
wasn't related by blood,
I was somehow wrong.
So, you second-guess yourself
and where you belong.
Then, you start feeling lost.
It just sucks.
That about sums up the general
feeling, don't you think?
Or am I wrong?
You're not wrong at all.
Deep down, you
understand you're not
being logical, and yet,
knowing that doesn't
make it easier.
Eventually the way I chose
to look at it changed.
My mother is Miwa Asahina.
and she along with her
boys are my family.
It took time, but I got there.
Chii. The most important
thing isn't blood.
it's how you feel about
each other. It's the love.
[EMA]
The love?
[LOUIS] I don't remember
anything about them.
my birth parents, I mean. But,
with everyone in my real family,
I have tons and tons of memories
that I will cherish forever.
All the things
that have happened
from when I was
adopted until now.
I remember everything.
And you know what?
You're a part of
my family, now, Chii.
Will you do me a favor?
I want you to think
of me as your brother.
I want you to think of all
of us as your brothers.
I think we should go home.
Back to the condo.
Because that's where
our family is. Okay?
[EMA sighs]
Okay.
[LOUIS]
We're so lucky to have you.
Thank you for choosing us.
[gasps]
[JULI]
The Coalition to Protect Chii.
We spring into action
whenever needed.
Our only job is to protect you.
Juli is absolutely right.
Thank you, Louis.
You, too, Juli.
[JULI]
Chii.
Aw, look at him.
I think he can
finally relax now.
Poor lil' guy.
He didn't get much sleep.
He was practically beside
himself with worry last night.
Oh, I had no idea.
[LOUIS] I'm feeling
a little tired myself.
[yawns]
You're so sweet.
I didn't mean to make you worry.
I'm sorry.
[JULI]
Chii? Chii.
Huh?
It's me. Juli.
[gasps]
[JULI] It might be hard for you
to believe, but it really is.
Yes, I believe you.
It definitely seems strange.
but I know it's you
somehow. You're Juli.
I've always wanted to
see you face to face.
And I wanted you to see me as
a true companion for you.
Now my dream has come true.
First things first. I need
to apologize to you.
[EMA]
Apologize for what?
[JULI] Did you forget? I've been
around your entire life.
I know everything
about your past.
Huh?
[JULI] The truth about
your biological parents
is they passed away,
one after the other,
not long after you were born.
Rintaro stepped in
and took care of you
as if you were his own.
He raised you. He did
it all on his own.
and he gave you his whole heart.
He loves you, Chii.
Don't ever question it.
You are his real daughter.
I know it's been on his mind.
Telling you the truth.
He just couldn't figure out how.
He didn't want you
to doubt his love.
I didn't want that, either.
That's why I never said
anything. I couldn't.
Please believe me.
Our fault was
loving you too much.
For any grief I've
caused you, I'm so sorry.
[EMA] Mm-mm. I'm happy
that you told me.
But what really matters
is that you and Dad
are my real family, right?
Right.
All the time I've been
able to spend with you,
all the memories together:
they're incredibly
special to me, and now,
I'll treasure this
moment as well.
I can treasure this,
too. Oh, Juli.
You've always been
there by my side.
Thank you for that.
I love it when you smile.
It's all I ever
wanna see you do.
I didn't intend to say
any of this to you,
but there is something
I need you to know.
I love you, Chii.
[EMA] Was that just a dream?
It must have been.
[phone vibrates]
[gasps]
[RINTARO]
I heard what happened.
I'm sorry for putting
you through this grief.
I wanna sit down
and talk with you.
I'll be returning
to Japan soon. Dad.
[gasps] It's the same.
What I saw in my dream.
[EMA] I'm really sorry,
I never wanted to worry you.
We're just glad you're
home. Welcome back.
Hope you're feeling better.
I'll make a few
phone calls and let
everyone who's out
know that you're back.
I'm so sorry!
[IORI]
Welcome home.
Yeah, I'm glad you're all right.
We were all freakin' out.
Don't ever do that again, 'kay?
[WATARU]
Yay!
Be prepared to be
punished for worrying me.
Huh?
[giggles] It's a note from Futo.
[MASAOMI]
That's enough, Wataru.
Give her room to breathe.
I bet you're tired.
[EMA]
Oh, no.
You sure you don't wanna
rest for a little while?
I haven't made dinner yet,
so you have plenty of time.
[EMA] No, please.
Let me make dinner tonight.
I was hoping I could.
As you wish.
[WATARU] Yay! Can we have
haumburger steak please?
Wait!
I think I wanna
eat curry, too! I know!
How about hamburger steak curry?
Is that okay, can you make that?
Sure. I can make us
hamburger steak curry.
Yay! I don't mind
helping if you want.
[BOTH giggle]
The most important
thing isn't blood.
It's how you feel about
each other. It's the love.
[EMA] What Louis said
is right, and I think
that means I should
be open with everyone.
If I'm ever going to
be able to make memories
with them as a family, that's
the only way it can be done.
Yeah, okay!
I think I can do this!
Huh?
[BOTH laugh]
[JULI]
I love it when you smile.
It's all I ever
wanna see you do.
[EMA]
Hm?
[MASAOMI]
When Rintaro isn't here,
I have to be like
a father to her.
Well, that certainly
complicates things.
[TSUBAKI]
What's up, Futo?
You're wearing shades,
a hat, a mask.
[FUTO muffled] It's a disguise
to keep people from
recognizing me, naturally.
[TSUBAKI]
Just makes you look sketchy.
I don't see a disguise.
I see a pervert.
[FUTO]
Hey, don't call me that!
[TSUBAKI]
A pop pervert?