[KANAME]
You may be my stepsister now,
but that doesn't matter.
[IORI]
We can see each other.
Anytime we want.
[KANAME] There are no
taboos in love, after all.
[IORI] I know I shouldn't
have these feelings, but...
[BOTH]
I love you. And always will.
[EMA]
Of course we love each other.
We're family. Aren't we?
[EMA] I bumped into Futo
at a multi-media store
while I was out shopping.
This one looks good.
[EMA]
And then I called out his name,
forgetting that he was
a pop star heartthrob.
[EMA]
Oh, hey there, Futo!
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL 2A]
Oh my god, that's totally him!
[EMA] I just blabbed out a
teen idol's name in public.
And Futo was less than pleased
that his cover had been blown.
Yeah, just take responsibility
and rent these for me.
I'll be waiting at home.
[JULI hisses]
[EMA]
So I rented the DVDs he wanted,
and made my way back home.
Where Futo had even more
shocking things to say to me.
As punishment, you'll have
to do all sorts of things.
Most of them in your room.
[EMA gasps]
[JULI hisses]
[JULI]
Don't do it, Chii!
If you let a wolf like
this guy into your room,
who knows what he'll do?
[whispering] But he has
a reason to be upset.
The punishment
stuff's probably just
his weird sense of humor.
Open the door already.
I've got some movies to watch.
Sorry.
Wow.
You just do what
people tell you?
[EMA]
Huh?
Have a seat.
[JULI hisses]
You know what, hon?
That thing's hostile!
[hissing continues]
[FUTO]
Put it away somewhere.
All I need's a
scratched up face.
I'm a pop star,
in case you forgot.
Oh. Right. I guess
that makes sense.
[JULI] Are you kidding?
Let me outta here, Chii!
Chii? I can't protect ya
if I'm inside this bag!
I'm really sorry, Juli.
[JULI]
Can't breathe!
[FUTO]
So submissive.
One of my favorite qualities
in a new acquaintance.
Makes you more fun to torment.
[gasps]
Do something for me.
Would you pretty please?
[EMA] We're sitting
on my bed together.
Most girls would kill for this,
but it's so awkward.
[FUTO]
Hey.
Huh?
Do you mind if I move
closer to your side?
It's the angle.
I can't see the screen
as well from over here.
--[EMA] Really?
--[FUTO] There, that's better.
[EMA] You could cut this
tension with a knife.
[EMA]
It's so surreal.
A few days ago,
Futo was a handsome face
shining from the TV,
and now he's right here.
[FUTO] I gotta say,
that was incredible!
Right? I mean that last scene.
The one where
the main character
was just lounging around?
You don't even have
a clue, do you?
Non-industry types never do.
Acting natural in casual scenes
is always the hardest
part of the job.
I hadn't thought of that.
[FUTO] Scenes where all you're
doin' is walking and sitting;
those are the parts where
you see how good someone is.
Because if you're
faking your way through
the simple things,
it's transparent.
I've been trying to nail it,
and I've come up short.
So...
I'll keep practicing until
I'm just as good as him.
People say pop stars can't act.
I don't wanna
prove 'em right.
But you're never gonna
please everyone.
How insightful!
Shut up! Are you
makin' fun a' me?
[EMA] Mm-mm. It's just that
seeing you work so hard
to make your dreams come true.
I realized I should work
toward that too!
I think it's incredible
that you've found something
to feel so passionate about.
In fact, I'm a
little bit jealous.
You really are vacuous,
aren't you, little girl?
Huh?
[FUTO] Here I was,
actually considering
letting you off the hook
after this, but now...
It's hard to believe it didn't
catch my attention before.
How cute you are.
[EMA gasps]
You won't mind if I
don't call you my sister
very much, will you?
I guess that's okay.
Wait. No, I--
I mean...
[doorbell rings]
[YUSUKE]
Yo! You home?
They asked me to
give you this paperwork
for next week's
career counseling.
It's open.
[YUSUKE] Uh. I'm coming in.
I'm opening the door!
Hey, are you in here?
[FUTO]
Aw, man.
You're killin' the
mood in here, dude.
What the hell?
Futo, what are you doing?
A gentleman never tells.
Right? Sister?
[YUSUKE gasps]
[EMA]
You've got it all wrong.
We were just in here
watching a movie.
Let me go!
You're gonna mess up
my hair, you moron!
Shut up! I swear,
you gotta be watched 24/7!
[FUTO] 'Kay, later!
Let's do it again sometime!
[YUSUKE] Didn't I just
tell you to shut up?
[sighs]
Career counseling?
[JULI grunting]
Let me out!
[EMA]
Juli! I'm sorry!
Juli. Please don't be angry.
Bah! You let down
your defenses.
Perhaps today's incident will
teach you to listen to me.
It was weird, but I was
just about to stop him
before the door opened.
Huh! He's a savage,
incapable of reason!
Come down.
I'm going inside to help
Ukyo get dinner ready,
with or without you.
[JULI]
Hmph!
[EMA sighs]
Fine.
Ugh, what a headache.
That silly girl can be
a real pushover sometimes!
Greetings, Sir Juli.
Guardian of the
lovely Lady Chii.
And noble knight!
Well met!
And whom do I have the pleasure
of addressing down there?
[JULI yelps]
Oh. I-It's you again?
Don't sweat it, Chii.
It's been a long day.
[JULI]
I was wondering how
you knew my name for her.
So does that mean you can
understand what I'm saying?
[LOUIS]
Yup. You know what?
I just had, like, the best idea.
What do you say?
Care to negotiate?
[JULI]
A coalition to safeguard Chii?
[LOUIS]
Right. A protective alliance.
You and me.
[JULI]
Why would I trust you?
You're one of the
beasts I have my eye on.
Because, you know,
it's my job as her brother.
Don't you think?
Come on. Trust me.
[JULI] We have a
gentlemen's agreement.
[LOUIS]
Good. Pleasure working with ya.
[SCHOOL BELL ringing]
[YUSUKE groans] This is
pointless. I can't choose.
[EMA] Trying to pick
which school to go to?
[yelps] Uh. I, mean,
hello what's up?
What about you? Have you picked?
[EMA]
Well, more or less.
So is there something
you wanted from me?
Yeah. I wanted to ask for
your advice about whose name
I should put down
under "Guardian."
[YUSUKE]
Oh yeah.
Your old man's
been workin' overseas
for a while now, huh?
[EMA] He said he wouldn't
be able to make it back
until next month,
for the wedding.
[YUSUKE]
Gotcha.
So he's pretty much comin' back
just in time to get hitched.
Yeah. I can't wait
for him to get back.
It feels like forever
since I've seen him!
Right.
It's kinda the same for me
and my brothers sometimes.
For now, why don't you just
put Masaomi's name down?
I'll ask him to deal with it.
What? On my form?
He wouldn't mind?
[YUSUKE]
Hey, it's no problem!
Our parents are getting
married, aren't they?
We'll all be family soon enough!
So no sweat.
[EMA] Of course.
You're absolutely right.
Oh, I appreciate it, Yusuke!
Hey. No skin off my back,
not like it's a big deal.
Well, it is a big deal to me.
Anyway, thanks again!
I'll see you back at home!
Cool. See ya.
[YUSUKE] Good job, imbecile,
way to dig your own grave!
Once her dad marries
our mom, she'll be my...
Ugh! I don't wanna
think about it!
[MASAOMI] There we go.
Now it's official!
[EMA] I know you're busy.
Sorry if this is a hassle.
[MASAOMI]
No problem at all, little lady.
If there's anything else you
need, don't hesitate to ask.
Thanks. That's super
sweet of you.
You're happy.
These parent-teacher
conference things.
I never thought they
were a ton of fun.
Far from it.
They're actually boring.
It's been so long since
I had anyone around to go.
It kinda makes me feel...
I dunno, is
nervous-happy a thing?
Sure, Chii.
[door scrapes]
[KANAME]
Hello, and allow me to thank you
for looking after my
delinquent of a brother
and adorable little sister.
[YUSUKE] Whoa! What are
you doing here, Kaname?
[KANAME]
Masaomi got called away
for a medical emergency.
And I happened to be free, so
he asked me to fill in for him.
[YUSUKE] Wait. Why are the
four of us in one meeting?
[KANAME] No need to take
up any more time than necessary.
Isn't that right, Beautiful?
[KISHIDA]
Right...
[KANAME] Hm. My, my, you put
the college Suba is going to
down as your top choice.
Yes. That's right.
[KANAME] Did you choose it
because Subaru is there?
If that's the case, I'll cry.
No, it's coincidence.
[KANAME]
And Yusuke, you left your list
of preferred colleges blank.
You don't want to go to college?
I... want go there, too.
[KANAME]
Which one?
I just told you,
weren't you listening?
I'm going to the
same college as her!
[KISHIDA] Please,
there's no need to yell.
[UKYO] Oh, hi. I didn't
think you'd still be up.
Late night study session?
[EMA]
You got it.
And I needed something
to help wake me back up.
[UKYO]
Of course. Good luck.
[EMA]
Thank you very much!
[UKYO]
That really takes me back.
I used to do the same
when I was a student.
Here.
Remember, the most
important thing
is to try and stay healthy.
The wedding is coming
up soon, after all.
We don't want you
to catch a cold.
You're right.
Thank you for the advice.
[HIKARU giggles]
[EMA]
Who's that? She's beautiful.
[gasps]
Are you our new sister?
[sighs]
Nice to meet you.
My name's Hikaru.
I'm the fourth son
in the family.
Wait, did you say son?
[gasps]
[UKYO] Don't let the way
he's dressed fool you.
Hikaru is eccentric,
but still a man.
One of our illustrious 13.
[EMA] Oh. You're such
a pretty-- handsome man.
Welcome to the clan.
Glad you're here.
Oh! Thank you!
It's been interesting.
You should've called us.
instead you pop up in
the middle of the night.
And how long have you
been back in Japan?
Well, it's great to see
you too, big brother.
If you must know,
I was sent here
on a mission to deliver these.
But what are they?
They're packages sent with love.
[MIWA] Your father and
I bought these for you.
Thank you for giving me
the joy of picking out
a beautiful dress for
a beautiful daughter.
With love, Miwa.
[EMA]
Beautiful.
The perfect day for Dad
and Miss Miwa's wedding.
That special day
when we all become
one, big, happy family.
[doorbell rings]
Good morning, Chii. Big day!
And a perfect day it is!
[EMA]
Hang on a second.
Louis just called me Chii again.
How does he know that name?
[LOUIS]
Is something wrong?
No, not at all. Still waking up.
So, what brings you by?
Need my help with anything?
[LOUIS]
I'm here to help you out.
Let me do your hair! So, like,
you'll be in a
dress today, yeah?
I was thinking.
We could use colors
that compliment. Cool?
That is, of course,
if you don't mind.
Oh, I'd love that!
[EMA]
Hi!
You look lovely, darling!
Congratulations! Oh no,
I mean best wishes.
Wait, which one's
for the bride again?
[MIWA]
Oh, look at you.
Thirteen boys and finally
a girl to dress!
It's such a beautiful
gown, thank you!
I can't believe you had time!
It looks amazing on you!
I guess it was a
smart buy after all.
Right?
You're right! She looks great!
Oh, uh--
You look absolutely
stunning yourself, Miss Miwa!
You'll need to stop that
"Miss Miwa" stuff.
If it's okay with you,
you can call me Mom.
I'd like that.
Yes, ma'am.
[RINTARO laughs]
Give her a little time, honey.
I'm sure your dad's right.
Whatever you call me,
I can't wait to get to know you!
We'll talk soon.
Okay!
Miss Miwa seems
really wonderful!
And Dad looked so happy!
[JULI] Hm! I just wish that Miwa
lady would keep better tabs
on those mongrel boys she's
been not at all raising.
[laughs]
[door creaks]
[gasps]
Can I help you, Miss?
Oh, no, I'm fine.
This room's reserved.
Only family members are allowed.
Uh... Well, I am--
[TSUBAKI]
Yoo-hoo!
You're looking extra cute today.
Yes. Very fetching indeed.
You look so radiant.
You've made stealing
the spotlight obsolete.
You get results when
you make the effort, babe.
You are a vision of loveliness.
That's Louis for ya.
Expertly done.
Thanks! You look so cute, Chii.
Yeah.
Yo. What it do?
[WATARU] Sis! You look like
a fairy tale princess!
Little man's right!
Agreed!
In fact, I'd say that we're all
rather partial to your new look!
Hey!
[TSUBAKI] Oh look,
Natsume showed up after all.
You jerks did this
on purpose, didn't you?
[AZUSA]
Guilty as charged.
First impression's ruined.
Thank you so much.
Could someone explain?
I'm kinda lost.
[TSUBAKI]
This is Natsume.
Me and Azusa's little brother.
Technically, we three
are triplets.
[EMA]
Triplets?
Yup. Azzie and I here
are identical twins.
Natsume is our fraternal brother
from a different, less cool egg.
[MASAOMI] That's 13.
Now you've met everyone.
[WATARU] The Asahina brothers
are together again!
[EMA]
It's almost overwhelming.
We're all gonna be part
of the same family soon!
Dad and Miss Miwa had
such a wonderful ceremony!
I hope mine's just like it!
[JULI]
Whoa!
You're still too young for
something like that, Chii!
It's off the table until
way after college!
I didn't mean right now, Juli.
[EMA] I wanted to say
sorry for earlier.
[NATSUME]
No.
I should be the one
apologizing to you.
In fact, here.
It's my business card.
It's my personal number.
Just give me a call
if you need anything.
Like if Tsubaki's
being a total pain.
Okay, thank you very much.
[NATSUME]
You okay?
[EMA]
Well, it's just...
This is the company that
makes a video game series
I really like.
[NATSUME]
Wait.
Does that mean that
you're a gamer?
[EMA] Yes. Zombie Hazard
totally rules!
Well, uh, yeah!
Right?
It's my fave! I'm addicted.
I've beaten all of the games!
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to gush like that.
The most recent game's
definitely the toughest one.
If you beat that,
you got some skills.
Yeah?
I always enjoy getting
good feedback.
Thanks for that.
So! Would you be
interested in play-testing?
Of course! Can I
really do that?
Sure. No problem. Huh?
Look.
This might sound like
an odd question.
But how has Subaru
been doing lately?
I don't know. Can't say.
I only met him recently.
[NATSUME]
I heard he's not doin' well.
Got dropped as a starter,
having trouble focusing
on his game, stuff like that.
[gasps]
You've been around him
more than I have.
I was just hoping that you
might have noticed something.
[EMA]
Could it be?
Is that what he's
feeling bad about?
--[NATSUME] What is it?
--[EMA] Huh?
[phone ringing]
Ah, this is work,
I gotta take it.
Sorry to bother you
with brother questions.
Natsume Asahina.
Well, what'd the
Art Department say?
You're kidding.
[AZUSA, TSUBAKI]
And now, the lovely bride
and charming groom
will cut the cake!
[EMA gasps]
Hey, uh. Can we talk?
About what happened
on my birthday--
[EMA]
Please don't worry about it.
Because what
happened between us
doesn't bother me at all.
You didn't mean it.
The whole thing was an accident.
Look, I...
...owe you an apology.
I'm sorry.
[SUBARU]
I don't think you're a pain.
The things I said,
I didn't mean any of it.
Please believe me.
I do.
'Kay, I'll see ya later then.
--[WOMAN 3A] Ooh, I want it!
--[WOMAN 3B] Over here!
[WOMAN 3C]
That bouquet is mine!
Are you ready, ladies?
Here it comes!
[WOMEN gasping, giggling]
--[WOMEN] Aw...
--[applause]
[MIWA giggles]
[TSUBAKI] Congratulations!
That settles it!
We know who the
next bride will be!
Maybe I should throw
my hat in the ring!
[AZUSA]
Pump the brakes, Tsubaki!
Let's leave that
for another time.
Another time like tomorrow?
Now, now. Can we
give that a rest?
Well. Let's make
it official, gentlemen.
Though the setting may not
be the most appropriate.
Actually, this
setting's perfect. Eh?
Come on guys.
Let's keep this on track.
Shall we share how we feel?
Ready! Set!
[BROTHERS] Welcome to the
Asahina family, Sister!
[sighs]
[CATS meowing, purring]
Sorry. Bet you're hungry.
[NATSUME] Now, what am
I gonna do with this?
Guess I could find
somewhere to hang it.
Oh yeah.
I was gonna send
her some samples.
[gasps]
Subaru. So that's
what's goin' on.
[LOUIS] Hey, Azusa!
Is somethin' wrong?
[AZUSA]
When I woke up this morning,
I looked, but couldn't
find my glasses anywhere.
I'm not sure.
But I think that rascal
Tsubaki must've
hidden them from me again.
[LOUIS]
Here, I found 'em!
They were on top of your head.
[AZUSA]
Oh.