[HIKARU]
Whether you mean to or not,
you torment those boys.
[IORI] I know I shouldn't
have these feelings,
but they just keep
growing stronger.
[HIKARU]
You have every one of us
confessing our love for you.
[IORI]
I just can't help myself.
[HIKARU]
You're the one for me.
[IORI]
[IORI, HIKARU]
I love you.
[EMA]
Of course we love each other.
We're family.
[EMA] Our trip to Yatsugatake
came to an end.
And before I even
knew it, entrance exams
were just around the corner.
There are still so many
issues weighing on my mind.
But for now, I just need to
look ahead and try to focus.
And yet...
[groans]
Ugh. How did my mock
test grade go down so much
after such little time off?
[JULI] It's not the end
of the world, is it?
Practically every student
gets a D at some point.
I think Ukyo was
disappointed in me.
[JULI] Hey, it's perfectly
normal to bomb the dry run
but ace the real deal.
That's part of the
"entrance exam blues."
Really? And how many
exams have you taken?
Uh--
[doorbell rings]
[EMA]
Just a second!
Yes?
Hey. Can you spare
a couple minutes?
[EMA]
Sure! What's up?
Just thought of a way to
help out with your studies.
I made us brunch!
[EMA] Wow! You really
made all of this?
[UKYO] Yes. And since I
had a few assistants today,
I thought it'd be
appropriate to go all out.
Yeah, we practically worked
our fingers to the bone,
you old meanie.
And yet, somehow,
you still proved
completely useless.
[EMA] Sorry, this was supposed
to have been your day off.
Today was my turn to
make lunch for us.
Hey, not a problem.
The entrance exams are less
than a week away, after all.
We really don't mind picking up
a bit of the extra slack
if it helps you and Yusuke out
over the next couple of days.
So why do I feel
like I had to do
just as much work around
here as I normally do?
[TSUBAKI]
That's right!
I meant to wish you luck on
your entrance exams too, bro.
[AZUSA] You could sound
a bit more sincere.
Even if his chances are abysmal,
let's be supportive.
[YUSUKE]
Dude!
[giggles]
Yay! She smiled!
We totally did it, guys!
All right!
[EMA]
What?
You were super sad
when your test results
came back with such a low grade.
So we all decided to
try and cheer you up.
Wataru!
[UKYO, TSUBAKI, AZUSA groan]
Thanks, guys.
I really appreciate it.
You've all been so
considerate of my feelings.
But I'll be just fine, promise.
I've applied to a safety school.
And I can still get
a major in the field
I wanna study there. So it's
no big deal in the long run.
[YUSUKE]
Now wait a damn minute!
Second best is unacceptable!
Don't give up before
you've even tried!
[EMA]
I didn't mean that.
There are always things
that won't go your way,
that's just part of life.
But no matter how
hopeless it might seem,
there's always a chance
if you don't give up.
I'm applying to Meiji
with no safeties.
If I study hard enough,
they have to take me.
I know you can get in, too.
For someone who barely passes
any of his evaluations, I really
admire your new attitude.
Are you really going
for your top choice,
with no safeties?
That sounds incredibly reckless,
which is what we've come
to expect from you.
Well, we're all pulling
for you, regardless.
Great. Thanks for the
vote of confidence.
I'm gonna do it just
to spite you guys.
Yusuke's right! I refuse
to give up, too!
I'm going to study hard,
and get into Meiji with you!
Yeah? Let's do it! Together!
[WATARU]
College? You? Yeah right!
Wow. Thanks, kid,
I love you, too.
Lookie.
To help out, I made you
this super cool present.
You made a present?
Yup! Here you go.
That's the Helper Ticket.
And the Play a Game
Together Ticket.
One more. Here you go!
The 100 Smooches Ticket!
[YUSUKE coughing]
Oh uh, it's the
thought that counts?
Why you look weird?
What happened?
[EMA]
Cool. All done.
I don't know.
Seems like it would create
an emotional disconnect
from the previous scene.
Yeah.
This whole chunk has nothing
to do with the through line.
I'd see what the director
thinks about it.
[TSUBAKI] Guess that's
the only shot I've got.
Director's a real 'auteur' type.
I don't wanna screw anything up.
[footsteps scuffing]
--[AZUSA grunts]
--[TSUBAKI] Hm?
[EMA] Hi guys.
Are you two heading out?
[AZUSA]
Yeah.
We've both been scheduled
for some voice-overs.
The studios are in
the same direction.
So, we figured maybe
we could share a ride.
[TSUBAKI]
Besides.
I needed to go over the
script a few times more.
So I asked my dear brother
if he could give me a lift.
[EMA]
Well, that's sensible.
[gasps] Hang on a sec.
There. Sorry.
I need to step outside
and call the director.
Sure thing.
I'll grab the keys
and follow along.
Cool. Thanks. Ciao!
[EMA]
Yeah! See ya later.
[AZUSA] Tsubaki's certainly
changed, don't you think?
It all started when I was sick
and he took over my role for me.
It's like he's way more serious
about his acting since then.
And the people at the
studio are noticing.
I'm glad for him.
Being able to make your own way
in the job of your dreams
is totally awesome.
I've seen how hard you've
been studying, you know.
Keep up the good work,
and you'll be
the same as him one day. Right?
Right. I won't let you down.
I've never seen Tsubaki
so focused before.
It's bad luck that your health
kept you from playing the part.
But I'm excited he'll get to
play the role he always wanted.
[AZUSA] Oh. Is that what
you think happened?
I believe there's an
entirely different reason
for his new found drive.
No. The person
Tsubaki has become
is more captivating
than he ever was before.
So when you think of him,
see the man he is now,
not the boy he used to be.
And, who knows?
That might push me to
accomplish more as well.
[EMA]
Um, okay.
[AZUSA] I hope you'll take
that into consideration.
When you find an answer to
the way we feel about you.
[gasps]
[AZUSA] I won't press
you for a response
until after the exams.
And no matter what
answer you give,
I'll accept it with grace.
[sighs]
[EMA]
Subaru? You look nice.
Hey, have you got a minute?
[SUBARU]
I told you before.
I was approached by
a scout for the pros.
I've decided to
accept the offer.
[EMA gasps]
[SUBARU] They asked me to
come to their headquarters.
So I'm heading off to Kyushu
for final negotiations.
I'm leaving today.
Congratulations!
I'm so happy for you!
Looks like I'll have
to be out there
for quite a while.
And by the time I get back.
You'll be finished
with your exams.
I feel bad because
you're applying
for my school, but I won't
be able to help out.
Oh, it's fine. Please,
don't worry about it.
[SUBARU] Listen. I know
your scores dropped.
Don't let that get you down.
All of the hard work you've
put in will pay off big time.
Thanks.
It may be tough, but I
know you'll get by.
Just stay strong.
And that stuff with me?
It can wait until you're done.
[gasps]
So. Yeah. I should get going.
Oh. Sure.
[EMA]
Have a nice flight. And...
Good luck to you, too.
Thanks a lot.
[giggles] I'll do my very best.
I owe everyone that much.
[EMA]
And at long last.
The day of the entrance
exam was upon us.
[JULI]
Chii!
[EMA]
What is it?
Do you have your
exam pass ready?
[EMA]
I've got it.
What about your pen case?
Did you grab that?
Yes! I've got it right
here, okay? You see?
[gasps] Oh no, it's empty!
[JULI]
Now calm down, Chii!
[EMA] That's pretty rich
coming from you!
--[doorbell rings]
--[JULI] Here's a pen.
--No, wait, that's me!
Oh. Coming!
Good morning! You ready?
I guess so.
[JULI]
Hm?
Good luck.
I have to head out
for the day, now.
But I wanted to come by
and be supportive!
Thanks. I really appreciate it!
[JULI] Me too! She needed
some good vibes!
What's wrong?
Louis?
Stray hair.
Huh?
There. I'm all done.
I like having my hair in place.
Makes me feel sharper.
[EMA laughs]
Heh. That's Louis for ya.
He understands all that
self-confidence crapola.
Yep. Yep.
[LOUIS]
And there's this.
It was sitting in
front of your door.
[EMA]
How pretty. Iori?
[LOUIS] An iris. In the
language of flowers.
"Faith in good things to come."
[EMA chuckles]
Your packed lunches.
[YUSUKE]
Thanks a lot, Ukyo.
[EMA]
Thanks.
Just try to keep yourselves
relaxed, alright?
But don't be so relaxed
that you can't
give it everything.
And do double-check your
work for random mistakes.
Ah.
They say you should always
go with your first instinct
when taking a test.
Either you studied
well and know it,
or you didn't and don't.
[UKYO] What do I know?
I'm just a lawyer.
[HIKARU] Well. Our charming
sister is one thing.
But you'd better go over your
work with a fine-tooth comb.
Thanks for the confidence.
[phone rings]
[NATSUME]
It's finally time.
When you're done,
I'll have a reward for you.
So good luck.
Thanks, Natsume.
[phone rings]
Who is this? Hello?
[FUTO]
Nice.
I'm puttin' in the effort to
call during my break at work,
the least you could do
is pick up faster.
[EMA]
Futo?
[FUTO]
If I remember correctly.
You're takin' your
big test thing today.
And so, my gift is the honor
of hearing my sexy voice.
But if you fail, you can
always stay back another year.
Then you and I can
have a lot of fun
being in the same
class together.
Great. Did you just
call to tease?
Are you still there?
Seriously though, good luck.
I'll be cheering you on.
[phone clicks]
[EMA] Can't believe he took
the time just to call me.
I wonder if he really
meant what he said,
or if he was just
teasing me again.
[YUSUKE] Let's get going
before we're late!
[EMA]
'Kay!
[EMA] They each have
different ways of doing it.
But everyone's rooting for me.
Because that's what families do.
They support each other!
And once the college
entrance exams are over...
[EMA] ...that will open the door
to a whole new adventure.
[EMA]
The test is over and done with.
But I can't relax until
the results come in.
[sighs]
[KANAME] What an adorable sigh
you have, Little Sister.
[EMA gasps]
Don't scare me like that!
I didn't know you'd gone out.
[KANAME]
Yeah.
I've got a thing or two
on my mind at the moment.
[EMA]
Hm?
But tell me.
I'd like to know why you were
sighing like that just now.
[EMA] It's no big deal.
It's just that,
every time I think about
my test results,
I get so nervous.
[KANAME]
About failing?
It could really go either way,
as far as I could tell.
[KANAME]
Gotcha.
Allow me to offer you
a tiny bit of advice.
Though it has been
quite a while.
Almost a decade since my exam.
But anyhow, if things
don't work out.
You can always come to
my place. How's that sound?
Oh, don't you worry!
I'll be fine.
I'm pretty sure the
flower Iori gave me
will bring me more than
enough luck to pass.
Iori, huh?
[EMA]
Yeah. He gave me an iris.
Apparently in the language
of flowers it means:
"Faith in good things to come."
[KANAME]
I see.
Is there something the matter?
[KANAME] Nothing. Right.
I'm heading inside.
It's cold. You should
head in too.
Don't wanna get sick.
[EMA]
Sure. In a bit.
The language of
flowers is tricky.
That iris you gave her.
It has another meaning than
the one she's been told.
"I will risk everything.
All for your love."
Yeah. That was what I needed.
When we're done here,
we should try
some of the other games.
[NATSUME]
Just let me have this break.
It's hard to lose
ten rounds straight
on a game I helped develop.
That one's pretty tough.
I think we're probably
gonna have to lower
the difficulty of the next one.
[EMA]
No! That's boring.
Too bad. Speaking as
a game maker,
if we used you as the benchmark,
the average player
couldn't keep up.
Oh, I'm sure that's not
true. I'm not that good.
[NATSUME] You beat me,
so I'd rather say
you are if that's okay.
[giggles]
[NATSUME]
This is nice.
I'm glad you agreed
to come here.
[EMA]
Yes! Very nice.
I've been dying to
check this place out
ever since I heard they opened!
Yeah, I figured.
Told you I had a
reward for after exams.
And, there was something I
wanted to talk to you about.
[EMA]
Oh, really? Like what?
Are there other games you
wanted to take a crack at?
Huh? Well, let's see.
Yeah, there are like, a ton,
so it's hard to choose just one.
Whatever we miss,
we can come back and try.
[EMA]
Great!
And we should come here
with everyone next time!
That last game we played
can have ten people
at a time playing
against each other!
Good grief.
Are you planning
on beating the crap
out of the whole
family next time?
It wouldn't be a
total beat-down.
Yusuke might give me a
good run for my money.
Oh! I bet Subaru's
probably not bad either!
He made it into
the pros, after all.
So he's gotta have
pretty good reflexes.
The pros? What're
you talkin' about?
What? Wow. Oh, boy.
Subaru is negotiating with
a professional basketball
team right now.
I'm sorry. I thought you knew.
I didn't.
I guess he has
been workin' hard.
[NATSUME]
We're here. Is this good?
[EMA] Sure! Thank you so
much for today's treat.
I had a really great time!
Next round, we celebrate
your results!
[EMA] Don't say that,
you'll jinx it! But really.
This whole entrance
exam experience
has just been so stressful.
It makes me appreciate
how nice it is
to have such sweet brothers.
Oh, that reminds me.
Wasn't there something
you wanted
to talk with me about?
Nah. Maybe another time.
I'm just glad I got you
to unwind a little bit.
Anyway, you better get goin'.
I'll see ya later.
Okay.
[EMA]
I hope everything's all right.
I wonder what he wanted
to talk about.
[NATSUME grunts]
[gasps]
[NATSUME] I'm sorry.
I couldn't help myself.
I can't stifle it any longer.
[NATSUME] I don't know if this
is the right thing or not.
But, I refuse to
ignore these feelings.
Listen. I think I'm
--falling in love with--
--[door slams]
[SUBARU]
What the hell is this?
[EMA]
Subaru?
Back off!
Hey, calm down.
Didn't you hear me?
I said back off!
--[NATSUME grunts]
--[EMA gasps]
Are you all right?
[SUBARU]
What were you playing at?
What'd you try to do to her?
[EMA]
Subaru, you have to stop this!
Natsume was just--
It's fine.
[gasps]
Okay. I'll come right out
and say it, then.
I think I'm falling
in love with you.
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
You're joking.
[NATSUME]
Not at all.
[SUBARU]
There's no way I'm going to lose
to some worthless
quitter like you!
What was that?
[NATSUME]
I was in track and field
all the way up until college.
But in the end, I chose to quit.
Subaru always looked
up to me before that.
I tried to play it cool,
act like I didn't miss it,
so he wouldn't feel bad.
But I think pretending
not to care
just made him
disappointed in me.
And now,
my not so little brother got
called up to the Majors.
Guess that's the payoff
for all his hard work.
I think you might've been a
pretty big factor in it too.
No way. I didn't
do anything at all.
[NATSUME] Either way,
I'm not giving up this time.
I can't.
No need to answer now.
You can take
your time. I'm here.
[doorbell rings]
[EMA]
Subaru? It's me.
[gasps]
You there?
[SUBARU]
Look, I'm sorry.
But could we do this
some other time?
I'm still worked up.
I just thought
you should know
when I told Natsume
you were going to be
a professional basketball
player, he was happy for you.
[gasps]
[EMA]
I figured you might wanna know.
See ya.
[SUBARU grunts]
[SUBARU]
Damn it.
[chipper music plays]
[door clicks]
[grunts]
[door scrapes]
Huh?
[EMA]
Subaru, wait!
[SUBARU]
Oh, hey.
What's wrong? Are you leaving?
To get ready for the pros,
I need to train.
I'll be gone a while.
[EMA]
But, why?
I had no idea.
Never knew how
Natsume felt about me.
Until you told me yesterday.
I pushed my big brother away.
All because I
couldn't understand.
And then I went and
sucker-punched him
in front of the woman I love.
I'm such a stupid jerk.
So I want you to
forget about all of it.
[EMA]
What?
Please forget about all of the
things I said to you before.
The way I am now,
there's no way I could
ever make you happy.
Subaru...
[water splashes]
Man, I can't relax!
Just announce
the results already!
You're fine. You did
everything you could.
You'll get accepted,
then tell her.
You love her!
[HIKARU]
I can't hold back any longer!
When I see her,
my heart starts
pounding in my chest!
[YUSUKE]
Hikaru, bro.
Don't tell me you've got
feelings for her, too!
[HIKARU] It's time I worked up
my nerve, and asked her.
"Can I borrow your
school uniform?"
[YUSUKE]
That's what you want?