True, I may be the
hopeless eldest son.
But you make me want
to be a better man.
And I may be the
youngest brother,
but I'm not a
little kid anymore!
We can see each other
whenever we want.
Maybe when I grow up,
I'll be able to
take care of you!
[MASAOMI, WATARU]
I just want you to be happy.
Because I love you.
[EMA]
Of course we love each other.
We're family. Aren't we?
[EMA] They all seem so
shiny and new, don't they?
Every single one
of them has 'noob'
written all over their faces.
[giggles] I bet two years ago
the seniors were saying
the same thing about us.
[AZUSA]
Working hard, I see.
[YUSUKE]
Huh?
What? Azusa?
Yes. Top of the morning.
What's wrong? Do I have
something on my face?
Uh-- No!
It's just that you look much
more formal than usual.
Yeah!
Why are you all
dressed up like that?
And more importantly,
what the heck're you doing here
in the first place?
[AZUSA] I hadn't planned
on being the one
who needed to come
to school today.
But I didn't have
much of a choice.
Masaomi, Ukyo, and Kaname
all claimed to be
too busy to make it in time.
Apparently, I'm fourth in
line to play your guardian.
You're our guardian? For what?
Azusa, come on.
You're sorta confusing
us here, dude.
I don't get what's
confusing about this.
Um, maybe give us a hint?
[FEMALE STUDENTS shrieking]
Uh, what the hell?
Surprise. Does it
make more sense now?
He's here.
[FEMALE STUDENT 6A]
Isn't that Futo Asakura?
[FEMALE STUDENT 6B]
No way!
[FEMALE STUDENT 6C]
OMG! It is him!
[EMA]
It's Futo.
[YUSUKE] Aw, you have got to
be freakin' kiddin' me, man!
Hey, good morning, guys!
I am super-psyched about
my first day at Hinode High.
My name's Futo Asahina.
I should be in the
roster here. Right there.
[gasps] Why do I have the
feeling something really bad
is about to happen?
Chii! Please stay safe!
Chii!
[sighs] That was weird.
Were you as shocked as
I was, or did you know
Futo decided to come here?
You kidding? I had no clue
this was gonna go down.
Man, as if being
related to a pop star
isn't punishment enough.
Sometimes I really hate
that smarmy jerkwad
No, you don't.
This is Futo's first
day of high school,
so why don't we partner up
to show him around and stuff.
It might not be what we wanted,
but at least we're almost
out of this place.
Yeah. I guess that's
one way to look at it.
Speaking of what we want,
didn't you go to Subaru's
game the other day?
How'd that go? It's not
really my business.
But ever since then,
things have seemed a bit off.
The way you act
around each other.
It's different.
[EMA]
Oh?
[NATSUME]
So how 'bout it?
Are you goin' out
with Subaru or what?
[YUSUKE]
Hey, you all right?
Of course. Everything is fine.
I think I'll to check on
things at the auditorium!
[YUSUKE]
Oh? Cool. Right on.
[sighs] Everything is fine.
I'm pretty sure I know
what I wanna do.
[FUTO grunts]
Oh, no. What's wrong?
Are you okay? Futo--?
I think he just dozed off.
No, we shouldn't. We can't.
He's talking in his sleep.
Stop it. If you do that.
I'll lose my self-control.
It's not right.
Fine, then grab
the whipped cream.
[EMA]
I don't think I wanna know
what he's dreaming about.
But... It kinda
looks like it hurts.
You're my sister!
Huh?
[FUTO]
We can't do that.
Hey, Futo?
[FUTO chuckles]
Tell me, was my
acting convincing?
Wait. You were just acting?
Aren't you supposed to be
at the entrance ceremony?
[FUTO]
It was Snore City, so I left.
But running into you out here
beneath the tree's shade
was definitely a happy accident.
Say, did you notice?
I've been getting
taller recently.
Know what that means?
Now I can do this!
Much better for my leading
ladies, don't you think?
I... guess so.
You wanna run,
now's your chance.
So? You're not gonna run, huh?
Then I guess that means you
don't mind if I make a move?
[FUTO]
Phoo...
I love anticipation.
Your school life is about to
get 50 shades more exciting
than it ever was before
I showed up, my dear.
Now then.
Better get back
before I'm missed.
See ya later. If you're lucky.
What have I gotten myself into?
[ALL giggling]
[YUSUKE] Well I didn't
think it was funny!
You have any idea what
a shock it was? Jeez!
[HIKARU]
Futo must've had his reasons
for keeping it under wraps.
Plus, he's always loved
to make a grand entrance!
[EMA] Azusa showed up
looking so handsome, too.
The whole situation
was overwhelming!
Apologies!
It never occurred to me
that you and Yusuke
had been left in
the dark about it!
Masaomi? Whatcha got?
Have a look.
Photos our newest
family member took
during the entrance ceremony.
[KANAME]
Nice. That's a pretty good shot!
Hey, Little Sis. I'll be
your artist's model anytime.
If it's just you, me,
and the camera.
I can go nude, as long
as it's tasteful.
--[gasps]
--[hisses]
I wanna look at the pictures
she took too, Kaname!
Let me have a turn! Come on!
It's my turn to see the
pictures on her camera!
--It's my turn!
--Fine, fine. Take a look.
[KANAME] Here you go,
just don't break it.
[grunts]
[WATARU] Yay! I'm gonna
go cuddle with Juli
and look at 'em!
I hate to say this,
but we really needed
a girl around for this stuff.
Without Mom here these days.
No one thinks to take pictures
of Futo's first day
of high school, or very
much else for that matter!
I always keep that
camera with me.
I was thinking about
printing some of them out
and giving them to you.
Along with wedding and
cherry blossom picnic photos.
[MASAOMI] Perfect!
I think that's a great idea.
We should put some
of them up in here!
[EMA]
What? You really want to?
Absolutely!
We should have some
of Mom's old frames
lying around this place.
I'll start looking for them.
[EMA]
Okay!
[MASAOMI]
Hm. Yeah. A little dusty, but.
[EMA]
Wow!
And take a look at
what else I found
lying around in here!
[TSUBAKI] The party's here,
guys! Well, well, well.
Looks like you already
started without me.
Are we having fun?
[EMA]
Yeah!
[MASAOMI]
Welcome home!
[WATARU]
We found photo albums!
Aw! How cute! Is that
you holding baby Yusuke?
Yep, that's right.
[gasps] What else you
do you have in there?
What about me?
Show my pictures!
[MASAOMI] I think all our
photos of you are in this album.
[WATARU] Hey, there aren't
very many pictures of me.
You haven't been
alive long enough
to have that many taken.
[EMA]
Huh. There's Natsume and Subaru.
Yeah. Back when
Subaru was younger,
those two kids were
practically inseparable.
Really? I had no idea.
What's this? It was just
loose between the pages.
Is that Tsubaki?
[MASAOMI]
No, I think it's Azusa.
[KANAME] We don't have
too many pictures of him.
Alone, that is.
[HIKARU]
Growing up, Tsubaki and Azusa
were stuck together like glue.
You're the one who took this,
aren't you, Tsubaki?
See? It's blurred.
That's why it wasn't
kept in the sleeves.
[TSUBAKI]
Hey. I was a kid!
[HIKARU] I guess Mom
couldn't bring herself
to throw it away.
Oh, come on. Maybe I
was being artistic.
It's got a certain style to it.
Oh, I like it.
After all, I don't have
too many photos of myself
from when I was little.
Let alone enough for an album.
I admit, I'm a little
jealous. Must be nice.
I hope we can pack
more albums full
of happy memories like these.
Do you want to keep it?
That photo of me?
[BROTHERS gasp]
Huh?
Oh. That wasn't what
you meant, was it?
Sorry if I made things weird.
No. I'd like that.
But is it really okay
for me to keep it?
[gasps]
Of course it is! If you
want it, then it's yours.
What do we have here?
Are you trying to
steal her heart?
[AZUSA]
What? No, man, you're demented.
Azusa, you sly old dog!
What's going on?
[laughs]
[AZUSA]
Well. Good night.
[TSUBAKI] Don't let 'em bite.
Hey, so listen.
Just so you know.
I'm not backing down
when it comes to her.
Not for anybody in the world.
Not even for you, Azusa.
Do you understand?
Very well, then.
[giggles]
[JULI]
You look pretty chipper, Chii!
Yeah. I am.
Growing up alone I
never had any siblings.
Much less pictures
of them as kids.
It just makes us
feel more like family!
[JULI yawns] That's nice.
Just don't stay up too late.
[EMA] We need to finish those
leeks before they go bad.
Maybe I'll make some
leek and tofu miso soup
for dinner tonight.
[SUBARU]
Why are you here?
[NATSUME] I do like to come
home every once in a while.
Plus I have something
I need to drop off.
Why are they just
standing there outside?
So then, how are things?
None of your business.
Look, I know you're holding crap
I did in the past against me.
But I don't know what
I'm supposed to say
that's gonna change that.
And the problem
you've got right now,
you did to yourself.
If you plan on seriously
pursuing basketball,
you need to give it
your full focus.
Don't let unnecessary
things distract you.
Unnecessary things? What do
you know about who I am?
And what the hell makes
you think I care at all
what you have to say about me?
Maybe what you're
really saying has less
to do with me,
and more to do with her!
[gasps]
[sighs]
Oh, hi.
[EMA] Uh, I, I'm sorry.
I overheard your conversation.
[NATSUME]
Oh. That's mildly awkward.
Anyway, I'm actually
here to give you this.
See? A sample of our new game.
[EMA]
Nice. Thank you, Natsume!
And about what Subaru said.
Don't worry about it.
He's just a bit upset.
Oh right. I figured as much.
Well, I'm not worried about it.
I appreciate you making
this less awkward
than it could be. Thank you.
Remember, if you need
anything just call me.
[sighs]
[IORI]
What are you sighing about?
[EMA]
Iori.
I take it you were
in the back yard,
checking on your garden?
[IORI]
Yep. Checking and watering.
Forget that. Is something wrong?
Yeah, it's Subaru and Natsume.
Bit of drama
between those two?
Don't worry about them.
In the end, they're brothers.
[EMA]
I suppose.
Come on, smile.
Smile and I promise to bring you
some more beautiful flowers.
It's a deal.
[EMA]
Oh, hi, Azusa.
[AZUSA]
I'm glad I caught you.
Do you have just a second?
[EMA] Yeah, sure.
Just let me get the door.
I wanted to come by and
give you a little something.
It's not much, but I thought
you might like it.
[EMA]
Huh?
It's a book!
A photo album.
You told us that you'd never
had one of your own, right?
So I wanted to
give you this one.
That was sweet.
[AZUSA]
It's a thank you gift.
Consider it a token
of my appreciation.
[EMA]
For what?
That anime project.
We're really starting
to pick up some steam.
Oh! That's really awesome!
[AZUSA] I know I made you
stress out about all of it.
I just wanted to
thank you and apologize.
You didn't need to.
I didn't do anything special.
No. If you hadn't
talked with me,
I would've turned down
a great opportunity.
Or worse, I might've ended up
hurting Tsubaki's feelings.
Without you, things might
not have worked out
the way they did.
We owe you so much.
If you say so.
But I should be thanking you!
It was very thoughtful
to give me this album.
Come to think of it.
This is the first time
we've talked like this.
Without my shadow
lingering about.
That's the hard thing about
having an identical twin.
[EMA giggles]
And it's not like we
haven't had time
to get to know each other.
I mean we've already been
living together for a while!
[EMA]
There's something about Azusa.
Whenever I talk with him,
it just feels so easy.
I wonder if this is what
having an older brother
is supposed to be like?
Hey man, sorry to call so late.
I didn't mean to make you worry.
Figured the least I could do
is talk with you myself.
Fill you in on
some of the details.
Well aren't we considerate?
I'm glad you guys worked
things out so amicably.
Are you sure you're
okay with this, though?
'Cause you should know.
They green-lit a game
based on the show.
Don't want you over-worked!
Hey, I make no promises here!
[NATSUME] Huh. Gotta say
I'm kinda surprised.
I thought for sure you'd
have turned down that role!
Yeah, I have her to
thank for it, too.
[NATSUME] Her? Wait a minute.
Did something happen?
A bit of this and that.
[NATSUME] Ah, jeez. I told her
to let you guys handle it!
[AZUSA]
She was just helping.
And you really listened to her?
Never known you to take advice
from anyone but Tsubaki before.
[AZUSA]
Is that a fact?
I feel like I've listened
to your attempts at advice
at least once or twice before.
[NATSUME] Now you're confused.
I don't give advice.
Hey, is it just me?
Or have you guys done
a little growing up?
What?
[NATSUME]
I dunno.
You guys just seem a
little different, is all.
Especially compared to when
I moved out of the condo.
I'm just wondering
if it's because of her.
Well, is that it?
[AZUSA] No. I mean that would
be weird, wouldn't it?
[snoring]
[EMA giggles] I can't even
get to sleep, I'm so happy.
I feel like a little kid again!
[TSUBAKI] Oh, hey! Can't sleep?
You mind if I join you?
Uh-- Let me get this
stuff out of your way
so you can work on
your new script.
You're treating that photo
with an awful lot of care.
The kind of reverence you'd have
for a picture of your boyfriend.
[EMA]
What? No, it's just that--
It should go in
the family album.
So that's the only reason?
You wouldn't lie to me, right?
[EMA]
Huh?
Can't you understand?
I need you, damn it!
I apologize for the
way I acted before.
I was selfish. And my
selfishness hurt you.
But time stopped the
first time I kissed you.
[EMA gasps]
[TSUBAKI] And scene!
Just wanted to run a few lines.
[EMA]
O-Oh, right.
[TSUBAKI] What clichéd,
hackneyed crap, huh?
[EMA gasps]
No, you know what,
I won't pretend.
I won't lie. I meant that kiss.
It wasn't a mistake or a
spur of the moment thing.
And those aren't
lines from a script.
Here, let me prove it.
[EMA gasps]
I love you. I adore you.
And I want you.
I won't let anyone
else have you.
[AZUSA, TSUBAKI grunting]
[TSUBAKI]
Azusa?
You asked me to meet you here
to do a read-through of that
new script you're working on.
Or did you forget?
There must be something
going around.
'Cause you forgot.
I won't give her up.
Not even for you, Azusa!
Yeah. You told me.
That means you're
doing this on purpose!
Yes, that's right. I am
doing this on purpose.
[gasps]
[AZUSA] Why don't you
go to your room, okay?
There's been quite enough
excitement for one night.
Yeah, whatever. Just forget it.
Tsubaki...? [gasps]
Goodnight.
[AZUSA sighs]
Are you okay?
Yes. Fine.
[EMA]
Are you okay?
You should go back
to your room, too.
Otherwise I might end up
becoming a hypocrite.
[EMA]
What?
[whispering] Damn it.
I'm just like him.
[EMA gasps]
[IORI]
Hello, Louis!
[IROI] Did you fall asleep
in the living room again?
Uh-huh. Nice photo.
Yeah. She was sweet enough
to put that up for us.
[FUTO]
Yo, Iori!
You're Mister Green Thumb,
right? What's that one?
[IORI]
Anemone.
In the language of flowers,
it means: "the pain of love."
[FUTO]
And that one?
[IORI] Kamchatka Lily
it means: "A curse."
[FUTO]
That one?
[IORI] Pincushion flower means:
"I have lost everything."
[FUTO chuckles]
New favorite!