[SUBARU] It's true.
I'm not suave or charming.
[NATSUME] At first. I thought
of you as a younger sister.
But somewhere along
the way, I realized
that I'd fallen
in love with you.
[SUBARU] It's not easy
telling you how I really feel.
But I love you.
[EMA] Of course we love
each other. We're family.
[EMA]
Oh!
What's the matter?
Did you hit your hand or
something else that hurts?
No. I'm okay, but,
there's no food for dinner.
[AZUSA] Well, that doesn't
sound like Ukyo.
[MASAOMI] He has had a lot
of trials to deal with lately.
[TSUBAKI]
Yeah, that can't be easy.
Being a big, fancy lawyer.
[EMA] Don't worry. I'll just
hop out to the store.
[gasps]
[TSUBAKI]
It's only gonna be us tonight.
Well, only us including Subaru.
Wanna go out to eat instead?
[JULI hisses]
[WATARU]
Did you say we're eating out?
At a restaurant?
I dunno. Most restaurants
are fairly lame.
Then, I have an idea!
Let's go have a picnic.
We can see the
cherry blossoms!
Yay, cherry blossoms!
Let's have a picnic!
Let's have a picnic...
That's fine by me.
A night viewing of
the cherry blossoms?
That doesn't sound bad.
I'd like to go,
but what about Subaru?
Oh, it'll be fine,
I'll let him know.
Don't you worry. And I
guess, while I'm at it,
I might as well
give Natsume a call.
Are you guys serious?
We can go?
Yes, I think we're all in
agreement that we can.
I can make some fried chicken
for the picnic, too.
Yay! We're gonna have a picnic!
We're gonna have fried chicken!
Fried chicken would
make the whole night
more delicious, so I gotta say,
yeah, we should
probably do that.
For God's sake,
don't forget the beer.
[phone rings]
[TSUBAKI]
You free right now?
[NATSUME]
Absolutely not.
[TSUBAKI] Oh, good.
We're all having a picnic
under the cherry blossoms,
so I'll just tell everyone
you're on your way, cool?
[sighs] Guess I'll go.
Even though I just went
and saw the cherry blossoms
with people from work.
[NATSUME] Why do I always let
him talk me into this crap?
[TSUBAKI]
♪ My sister crazy so crazy... ♪
[giggles]
[NATSUME] It's nice seeing
her look so happy.
[AZUSA]
Oh. Hey, Natsume.
[WATARU]
Welcome to the picnic!
[MASAOMI]
It took you long enough.
[NATSUME] Long enough for
that disaster, it seems.
How long have you all
been drinking, exactly?
♪ I'll take on the sorrow-- ♪
♪ give me pain tomorrow!
I don't... ♪
Don't be a downer. We never
get to do this stuff.
Why don't you try
to have some fun?
It's not our fault that
you don't get any
social interaction--
you wanted to move out.
Oh, shut up. I get
plenty of interaction.
[TSUBAKI laughs] Thank you,
ladies! I'm totally single!
Ah, jeez.
We're all exactly the
same age, but him?
He's like a teenager.
Well, there always has
to be one bad apple
in the bunch. Am I right?
[EMA] Here you go, Natsume.
Did you want some?
Yeah, thanks.
I realize you're busy.
I hope this picnic
wasn't a big hassle.
Nah.
[EMA]
Help yourself.
Everything except for this
we just picked up premade.
It's so good! Sis made the
--fried chicken herself!
--[NATSUME] Nice.
Okay, what're you lookin'
at me like that for?
I like it.
Well that's a relief. I was
starting to get worried.
[SUBARU]
You coulda texted me.
Oh, hey. What are you doing?
Drink run.
We were getting low,
so I offered to restock.
No prob. I can help you.
[EMA]
Oh... No, you don't have to.
I'm sure you must be
tired from practice.
[SUBARU] I'm good. Plus,
you could probably use a hand.
Where's your little sidekick?
I don't hear any hissing.
[EMA] Oh, you mean Juli?
Well, funny story.
[groaning]
Chii! Are you all right?
I can't believe you're
alone with those thugs!
This is the worst time
in the world to be struck
with a bout of food poisoning.
Talk about your big time
screw-ups, Juli!
[EMA]
Isn't it heavy?
[SUBARU]
Nope.
So, um...
What is it?
[SUBARU] About what
I said the other day.
[EMA]
Oh, that.
[SUBARU]
My next game.
I really do want
you to come see it.
I dunno.
[SUBARU] I guess I wanna
win in front of you.
[TSUBAKI] Hey, Natsume,
you drinkin' or what?
We got more comin', so we'd
better get rid of these.
--Come on, you know you want to!
--I'm cutting you off, Tsubaki.
You've had too much.
Oh. Hey, Subaru.
[TSUBAKI]
Hey, what's the big idea?
Why you guys
showin' up together?
Tell me it's a coincidence.
Yes, of course
it's a coincidence.
Um, guys. Where's Wataru?
[TSUBAKI]
Hey, that's a good question!
He was here just a second ago.
[AZUSA]
Huh?
Hello Ducky!
Quack, quack, quack!
Quack, quack, quack.
Oh no!
Are you asleep, Mister Ducky?
Quack, quack!
[quacks]
[yelps]
[ALL gasp]
[TSUBAKI]
Here we go. Heave-ho!
You're gonna have to
try harder than that.
[WATARU] Aww. Natsume,
look, you got all wet.
Why'd you wanna
jump in the water for?
Come on, didn't you know?
Natsume loves to go swimming.
For reals?
Yup, for real! See!
--[NATSUME yelps]
--[water splashes]
[TSUBAKI laughs]
[MASAOMI]
Okay, Tsubaki, that's enough.
[EMA]
Are you all right, Natsume?
I'm sorry, but I don't
think a handkerchief
is gonna be
much help for you.
[NATSUME]
Yeah, me either.
Was it really
a coincidence, then?
[EMA]
Huh?
Running into Subaru on your
way to get more drinks.
Oh! Yes it was,
of course it was!
Ah.
[AZUSA]
Natsume, Tsubaki's real sorry
he pulled that crap on you.
[NATSUME] Yeah, yeah.
No big deal I guess.
Hey, on the bright side.
you are literally a tall
drink of water, now!
[laughs]
You can shower at our
place before you go home.
Yeah. I think
I'll do that, then.
[EMA]
Wataru, did you get wet at all?
Nope! I'm not like Natsume!
I don't wanna swim in a pond!
[laughs] That's a
very smart decision.
[WATARU]
You mean Natsume's not smart?
[EMA]
No, that's not what I meant.
[gasps]
[NATSUME] So, Subaru. I read
the Basketball Monthly, too.
It's saying that you've
lost your form.
This is a crucial time.
What the hell's
goin' on with you?
Look, Natsume.
You have no idea what
it's like on my team.
I don't wanna hear it.
[EMA] I should probably
sweep this up later.
[EMA panting]
[elevator bell dings]
[EMA]
Who cleaned up?
Hey, did you already sweep up
all the flowers out here?
[SUBARU]
Just now.
[EMA] So, you're the reason
this area's always clean.
[IORI]
What's up, guys?
Oh! Hey, Iori!
How's your day going?
Something wrong?
[EMA]
Nothing.
I just felt bad because he
beat me to sweep up out here.
Don't feel bad.
Sweeping is what
Subaru's supposed to do.
[EMA]
What?
We're not sexist.
All the guys have chores
we do around here.
[EMA]
Really?
Even those beautiful
flower beds?
[IORI] Even those.
That's actually my job.
[EMA]
Wow, I had no idea. You're good.
They always have the
most gorgeous flowers.
Wait a minute.
When I first moved in here,
and I was in bed sick,
someone gave me flowers.
I thought they were
from everyone,
but did you arrange them for me?
[IORI]
Yeah. That was me.
You did? Thank you so much.
That was really sweet of you.
I thought that you
might like them.
It sounds like I was right.
I felt awful, but they
cheered me up.
Then, here.
Don't you know in
flower language a red tulip
is a "declaration
of love"! Who did it?
Who do I gotta fight this time?
Iori, but calm down,
it's a flower not an insult.
[JULI]
You're wrong!
The males in this house
flashing their mating rituals
at you is, in fact,
a huge insult!
Please, just let it go, Juli
[UKYO] I've decided to have
a feast tonight to make up
for the cherry blossom
picnic fiasco.
[EMA]
Sounds good.
But I don't know
how to cut this.
I've never handled such a
big piece of meat before.
Oh, don't worry.
I can take care of this.
Well, um,
I think I can probably do it,
if you don't mind
showing me how.
Light pressure with your
left hand to hold it still,
then, just follow the grain.
Easy for me to say,
right? I dunno.
It's kinda hard to
put into words.
Excuse me for just a minute.
It's like this.
[EMA gasps]
[UKYO] Hold the meat here
and the knife here.
That make sense?
See?
Once you can get the hang of it,
there's not that much to it.
Now, what are you two doing
fooling around in here?
--[EMA] Hikaru!
--[UKYO] You scared me!
[UKYO]
How long have you been there?
There's no need to worry.
I won't tell anyone
your little secret.
They won't hear you
were fooling around
in the kitchen from me.
[UKYO] Wait, what are
you talking about?
We weren't doing anything
even close to fooling around!
[HIKARU]
Then, by all means, explain.
You were holding
her hand, am I right?
I saw the back of your
neck was flushed.
What do you think
that was about?
[gasps]
I shoulda known!
Lawyers can never be trusted!
Juli!
[JULI] First the red
tulip and now this!
You damned brothers
are unbelievable!
[HIKARU]
Impressive. You're attended by
an exceedingly valiant
knight, Princess.
He's damn right
I'm your knight, Chii,
because if I wasn't, no one
else would be protecting you
from these ogres!
Especially with Louis
gone all the time.
[EMA] I keep telling you,
I don't need to have a knight.
[JULI]
Do too! You need me bad!
Hey, what's that
on your calendar?
What? Oh, that?
It's the day of
Subaru's next game.
[JULI]
And you're going?!
Are you planning
on cheering for him?
[EMA]
Mm-hm.
[JULI] Absolutely not.
I forbid you to cheer!
[EMA]
And why's that?
It's pretty normal to cheer
on your own family, silly.
Look, Natsume.
You have no idea
what it's like on my team.
I don't wanna hear it.
If I left now, I could make it.
[CROWD cheering]
[NATSUME]
We're only down by one.
[NATSUME] The coach didn't
even put Subaru in, damn it.
This is pointless.
[NATSUME]
Wait. Why's she here?
Huh?
Surprise. I didn't
know you were here.
Yeah, likewise.
You by yourself?
I didn't know you
liked basketball.
Oh, well.
The truth is Subaru invited
me to come watch him.
That's interesting.
Wonder why he asked
you here and not us.
Huh. I didn't think to ask him.
[horn blares]
[ANNOUNCER 5A] Meiji University
player substitution.
Number 7, Yamada, being replaced
by Number 14, Asahina.
[EMA giggles]
Go, Subaru!
Come on, Natsume,
cheer him on with me!
I don't cheer.
[CROWD cheers]
He did it! Subaru was
amazing, wasn't he?
There've been reports
he'd lost his form,
but he looks just fine to me.
[CROWD cheering]
[SUBARU panting]
[gasps] Oh no,
time is running out.
Come on, Subaru!
[SUBARU grunts]
[horn blares]
[CROWD cheers]
No way!
Subaru totally made
the winning basket!
[SUBARU laughs]
Yes!
Holy cow, I still can't
believe he made that shot.
If it weren't for Subaru,
they wouldn't have won the game!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I really don't know
a lot about basketball.
I may not be right.
Oh, no, you're right.
And there's no need to
apologize for being excited.
Uh-oh, looks like we might
be in for some rain.
You want a ride?
My car's parked nearby.
[EMA] Oh, no, thank you.
But I'll be fine.
Why are you being ridiculous?
You'd rather get wet?
No. Guess not.
[phone rings]
I've gotta take this
it's business.
You mind hangin' out here
for just a bit longer?
Yes. This is Asahina.
[SUBARU]
Hey!
[EMA]
Subaru!
Did you watch me?
I did. You were amazing.
[SUBARU]
Thank you. I owe it all to you.
[EMA]
What?
[SUBARU]
We won because you were here.
Because you watched the game.
You're why I played
so well again.
[EMA]
I-I'm sure that's not, um...
[SUBARU]
So, hey.
I have something that
I wanna ask you about.
'Kay.
[SUBARU]
It's just, um...
Do you have, like, a
boyfriend or whatever?
I need to know.
No, but I don't get
why that's important.
Well the thing is, I kind of...
I don't know how
to say this, but...
I want you, I need
you to be with me.
[NATSUME]
Subaru.
[SUBARU] Natsume.
What are you doing here?
I'm wondering the same thing.
Why are you out here?
Why aren't you
with your teammates?
Celebrating your big win?
You should be with
your team manager.
And with your coach.
Thanking them.
[SUBARU]
Yeah, I know that.
[NATSUME] Don't lose
your head just because
you had one good game.
Focus, man.
This is only round two.
You can't even
celebrate anything yet.
Get your butt back in there.
Save all this drama.
You can waste your time with
that stuff when you're great.
And you're not great, yet.
I don't have to take
this from some loser
who gave up on the game.
You may not have to,
but you will.
Because even as a loser,
I never pulled this crap.
[sighs] I'm so sick of this.
Think about what
I said earlier, okay?
So, how 'bout it?
Are you goin' out
with Subaru or what?
I don't-- I don't know
what's going on anymore.
I mean he's my brother.
This is so confusing.
I'm sorry.
The last thing I wanted
to do was to upset you.
I hope you can forgive me.
Now listen up, Jack!
Don't let that fact
that Chii cheered you on
go to your head, do ya feel me?
So guess what, Juli. Earlier?
I asked your best friend if
she wanted to go out with me.
[JULI hissing] Bastard face!
How dare you harass my Chii?
Well, how would you feel
if the two of us got together?
Homicidal!
[UKYO] Who's responsible
for making this rolled omelet?
[NATSUME] Um, I am.
What's wrong? Is it bad?
[UKYO] It is extremely bad.
You live alone, Natsume.
If you go around making
rolled omelets like this,
where does that leave me?
[NATSUME]
So you're saying it's good.