[KANAME]
Whenever you're upset.
Come and talk to me.
I'll ease your pain.
[CHIAKI]
However, if Kaname isn't enough.
Just ask for me.
I'll make it go away.
[RYUSEI]
Do you want something more?
I'll give you what
your heart desires.
[ALL] Forget all your
troubles at Club Buddha!
[EMA]
Thank you?
Kaname. Who are these two guys?
Are they your friends?
[EMA] After what
happened with Natsume.
I decided to make
an effort to be open
and honest with everyone.
That way we have a chance
of becoming a real family.
The truth of the matter?
Is the Asahina family needs you.
More than you seem to realize.
Everyone's having
these conflicts
because they all care
so much about you.
[LOUIS] Chii, the most
important thing isn't blood.
it's how you feel about
each other, it's the love.
[EMA] I can't believe
how quickly summer came.
The good news is,
Azusa's home, safe and sound.
Are exams getting you down?
Because I have a revelation!
A revelation?
What's that?
[KANAME]
Check it out.
You see. Since the overseas
trip got scrapped.
I thought some time away
might be just what we need.
[EMA]
Club Buddha? That seems weird.
It's not weird, it's Buddhist!
The head temple of our
sect is in Yatsugatake.
The Monks put on a little
festival there every year.
What about those two
guys posing with you,
you don't think that's weird?
[KANAME]
They're my colleagues.
Fellow Monks of the order.
Though naturally,
the most handsome,
dynamic and extraordinary
of the bunch,
is yours truly.
I'll chant by your
bedside all night long.
Big Buddha lovin'
till the sun comes up.
Hey, let's pass into
Nirvana together.
[UKYO]
You can be a man of faith or
a "gentleman of the night,"
but you can't
be both at the same time.
Take that, you perv!
The festival's legit.
We have stamps of approval
from the head temple.
It's all on the level, I swear!
Hey, relax.
It's just a little
summer festival,
there's nothing for anyone
to be worried about.
Yes, that's
exactly right!
I can always count
on you, buddy!
Can I go, please?
[MASAOMI]
Sure.
In fact, I'm thinking
it might be more fun
if we all went together.
I'm so disappointed.
Hey, I know this place.
It's close to our vacation home.
[EMA]
Vacation home?
Oh, you didn't
know about that?
One of our family getaways is
not too far from the festival.
[EMA]
One of?
[YUSUKE]
Yeah. We have several.
Wow.
[MASAOMI]
So, whaddaya say?
Should we go?
Sounds amazing.
I've never been on
a family vacation.
Hey, I'll come too!
Just to watch your back!
Good plan!
[MASAOMI]
Great! Let's let everyone know,
and whoever can make it
is welcome to join us!
Even though I still
hold my belief
that he's an impious pervert.
I suppose I'm okay with it.
[MASAOMI]
Kaname? Good idea.
Well, I see you've decided
to dress as a man again.
I look fabulous
either way, right?
True!
We'd better get going. If we
don't hurry, we'll be late.
We can't leave yet,
Subaru's on the phone.
Give him just a minute.
[AZUSA] Wait. I don't
see Kaname, either.
[UKYO]
He had a lot of work to do
to get the festival ready,
so he left yesterday.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
So, how was the call?
Eh. It was fine.
I said I wanted
more time to think.
All right then. Guess we'll see.
[EMA] Wonder what
they're talking about.
[WATARU]
Summer Festival here we come!
Hey. Have fun.
Wait. Aren't you coming with us?
I was. But then I
remembered I scheduled
my prep school summer course
at the exact same time.
[EMA]
Bummer.
Yeah, I know I wish
I could go with you guys.
But the truth is, my grades
aren't exactly up to par.
A vacation's fun and all.
But exams matter more.
Besides, I really wanna go
to the same college as you!
Well, good luck then.
Have a blast for me.
So, who's ridin' with me?
Got plenty of room in here.
[AZUSA]
Count me in.
Terrific. Anyone else?
[WATARU laughs]
I bet you wanna
ride with me. Yeah?
[EMA]
Sure?
[JULI snoring]
[JULI yelps]
Is something wrong?
No.
It's just that all of
a sudden, I feel like,
maybe I forgot something.
Huh?
I wouldn't worry.
Being out of your element
is part of the thrill
of going on a trip
to somewhere new.
Well, coming from a
seasoned traveler like you.
That certainly
makes me feel better.
By the way.
Do you mind if I
ask you something?
No. Please.
[HIKARU] Spoiler alert,
it's sorta personal.
When you spent the night
in Natsume's room,
nothing happened, right?
[AZUSA]
Dude!
Sorry, was that awkward
for me to ask?
I guess that depends
on what the answer is,
doesn't it?
Gee, thanks, bro.
No, obviously, nothing happened.
We're family, after all. Right?
Uh. Yeah!
You don't have to go home.
[HIKARU]
Hmm. One more thing.
I can't wait to hear it.
[HIKARU] Did something happen
between you and Azusa?
[AZUSA gasps]
--[NATSUME] Watch it!
--[car horn blares]
Things certainly do
seem to be lively
in the other car, don't they?
That's 'cause Hikaru's in there.
Yeah, for sure!
Hey, why are you asking that?
[HIKARU]
Why does it bother you?
I think that's a
very good question.
[AZUSA]
Look: nothing happened.
I was sick as a dog.
True, he was really wasn't well.
Of course!
Not to mention all the
nurses around everywhere.
But, if you wanted some privacy
there's always the rooftop.
[EMA, AZUSA gasp]
[AZUSA]
I'm through making apologies.
I love you, and I'm
not afraid to say it.
Oh. Come to think of it.
I'm so happy there's more!
Where's that little
creature of yours?
[gasps]
[JULI]
Chii. You forgot me!
How could you forget me?
[NATSUME] Sorry. But we've
already left the city.
[HIKARU] You guys really
are fun, you know that?
[gong rings]
Hurry up, Sis!
Come on, let's go!
Hey wait. Where's Ukyo?
He said he'd rather clean
the vacation house then be here.
At this "obscene,
ungodly festival."
You guys, I'm gonna
stop by and say hello
to Kaname's boss.
So, from here on out,
everyone's on their own.
[WATARU] Awesome, then I'm
gonna hang out with you, Sis!
[MASAOMI] Uh. Do you mind
looking after him for me?
No. Please!
[WATARU] All right! I'm gonna
have five shaved ice!
Well, it looks like the
youngest of the herd
is the most
aggressive one of all.
[SUBARU, AZUSA, NATSUME gasp]
Shaved ice is the
best thing ever!
That's your third one tonight.
Careful or you'll give
yourself a stomachache.
[WOMAN 10A]
Hurry up, guys!
[WOMAN 10B]
Aww, are we gonna miss it?
[WOMAN 10C]
Not if we move our butts!
What's up?
I don't know, let's see.
[CROWD squealing]
[FUTO]
Welcome to a special evening!
I'm Futo Asakura!
Let's keep this
energy up all night.
Whaddaya say?
[EMA]
It's Futo!
Futo live? This is so cool!
This crowd's really fired up.
[FUTO] ♪ somethin' in your eyes
that you cannot disguise ♪
[EMA gasps]
[EMA]
No. Not me? It can't be.
There are so many other
people in the audience.
[WATARU]
Hey, Big Sis.
What's the matter?
Is everything okay?
I don't feel good.
I think that last snow cone
was bad or something.
[gasps]
I feel bad for him.
Hopefully it passes.
Hey, lady. What's wrong?
Huh?
You couldn't find any nice boys?
What about me, then?
Oh. No thanks.
Club Buddha?
Hey. You're a Monk, right?
Then I guess you must
work with Kaname
at the Buddhist temple.
Kaname?
[KANAME]
There you are!
[EMA, CHIAKI gasp]
I'm really glad you
were able to make it!
What's the deal?
Please don't tell me this girl
is one of your customers?
No, Chi, of course she's not.
This young lady right here,
is my sister.
[CHIAKI]
Your sister?
Umm. Did you just call him Chi?
Oh yeah.
His real name's Chiaki but
that's a bit of a mouth full.
So we just call him Chi.
He's one of my colleagues
from the Buddhist temple.
[EMA]
Nice to meet you.
And it's nice to finally
meet the little sister
Kaname's so proud of.
It's true.
The adorable little sister
I'm so proud of.
[RYUSEI]
Well, well.
If it isn't number two and
number three together.
Fighting over a cute customer,
I have no doubt.
[KANAME]
Ah, hello, Ryusei.
[CHIAKI] As a matter of fact,
she's not a customer,
she's Kaname's sister.
[RYUSEI]
Is that right?
[EMA]
Yeah.
[KANAME]
Yes, that's right.
And this is Club Buddha's
number one Monk,
name's Ryusei.
[RYUSEI]
It's a pleasure. Oh, I forgot.
You should probably get back
to the main temple immediately.
Apparently, you both double
booked some clients.
[toung clicks]
You're in big trouble.
Why didn't you say
something sooner?
I'll see ya later on.
I gotta go fix this!
I hope he's okay.
[RYUSEI]
Oh, he'll be just fine.
[gasps]
You know.
When Kaname found about you,
he was beyond excited.
Was he really?
That's nice to hear.
[RYUSEI]
Must be exhausting.
The "good little sister" act.
Huh?
I'm a Monk, remember?
Might not seem that way.
Given how I look.
But I pick up on this stuff.
People's trouble and what not.
Um.
I'm not sure I understand
what you mean.
Right. Thing is, it doesn't
matter who you are.
'Cause we're all the same.
And we're all troubled
by the same thing.
Me too. It's human nature,
after all.
Know what it is?
Uh...
[RYUSEI]
It's love. Always love.
And it doesn't really matter
what form the love takes.
Since ancient times, it's always
been a thorn in our side.
Don't you agree?
I'm impressed, you totally
sound like a real monk.
[gasps] I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that to
sound so offensive.
There's no point in trying
to run away from love.
Instead, just be yourself
and confront it head on.
Because a family can
always survive the truth,
and that's what real love is.
[gasps]
[EMA]
Be myself and confront it?
I love you.
And I want you.
I won't let anyone
else have you.
[AZUSA] I love you.
And I'm not afraid to say it.
In the end, I'm no different
from my brothers
because it turns out that
I'm crazy about you, too.
I don't know how
to say this, but I,
I want, need, you to be with me.
Besides.
I really wanna go to the
same college as you!
[FUTO] Not by declaring
my undying love for you.
What I like, I take.
And I don't need to
ask your permission.
[EMA] Even though it
wasn't always right,
they were at least being honest.
Confronting their feelings.
The only who's
been running away,
is me.
[WATARU]
Sis! Hey!
Hey, Wataru. You feeling better?
Yep. A-Okay!
[RYUSEI]
Well. It was nice to meet you.
I wish you the best.
What's the matter, Big Sis?
[KANAME]
Thanks for everything, guys!
I seriously don't think the
Festival coulda gone better.
Thanks for bein' there,
Futo. Means a lot.
Next time, don't force
me into a booking
just because we're brothers!
It really pisses off my agents!
But you were the best
part of the Festival!
Like you know.
You left early!
Yeah, 'cause of the snow cones!
I'm very happy to hear you all
enjoyed yourselves today.
You shoulda come too, Ukyo,
you woulda had fun.
Yeah right, I'm sure
you mean that.
No kidding.
Hey. Why don't you two just
mind your own business?
No tellin' what'll happen
when we get together.
But it's always interesting.
We drivin' you crazy
yet, little lady?
Or is it fun?
Fun! Although...
[BROTHERS]
Hm?
I dunno...
I'd like to become
a part of this family
in a meaningful way.
[BROTHERS grunt]
But you already are.
Don't you know that?
You being here has been
a blessing for all of us.
He's right. You're the coolest!
That means a lot to me.
But, see, the thing is, I want
all of us to be even closer.
What gives?
Did you achieve some kind of
enlightenment at our temple?
[laughs]
[KANAME]
Trouble sleeping?
[gasps] Hey, Kaname.
I was just looking at
these beautiful stars.
You don't get to see stuff
like this in the city.
No, you sure don't.
[EMA]
Thank you.
I really appreciate you inviting
me to the Festival today.
It meant a lot to me
that you were there.
But, how about a
tiny favor in return?
[gasps]
[KANAME]
Let me hold you.
Stay here with me for a while.
[EMA]
Is that a sword?
Yeah. You ever heard the saying,
"the pen is mightier
than the sword?"
It means that in the end,
words will always
transcend violence. However.
In this world, there's
something even more powerful
than pens and swords and
everything else combined.
And that thing, is love.
[KANAME] Your love of family
came across back there.
Loud and clear.
But tonight, I need you
to know how I feel.
[EMA]
What?
You thanked me for
inviting you today.
But I'm the one who should
be saying "thank you."
You're precious.
I just hope you understand
how much you mean to us.
[FUTO] Your stupid speech
meant nothing to me.
'Cause you're mine.
Don't you know that?
It's your fault.
[FUTO gasps]
[FUTO breathes heavily]
[FUTO]
I tried. I really did.
I already gave you your chance.
See, the thing is, I want
all of us to be even closer.
[FUTO sobbing]
It's too hot.
[door slams]
You're up awfully
early, aren't you?
[FUTO sighs]
You mind turning that down?
I'll freeze my tits off in here!
[FUTO] What the hell
are you talkin' about?
This heat is killing me!
It's cool outside.
And the windows have
been open all night long.
[grunts]
Did something happen to you?
Mind your own
business! I'm fine!
I didn't do anything.
[yawns] Good morning.
Futo?
Well, the bratty one
is like a cat in heat.
The air's so clean
and refreshing.
I really wish Juli was
here with me though--
[gasps]
Hey!
You almost fell.
Yeah. Good catch.
Are you hurt or anything?
No. I'm okay, actually.
What are you doing out here?
Oh, uh. A little training.
But, we're here.
Do you have a minute?
Uh, I guess so, yeah.
I don't know if you
know this or not,
but Japan has a pretty decent
professional basketball league.
Yeah?
[SUBARU]
Yeah.
And, the thing is, I'm being
scouted by one of the teams.
That's neat.
Hey, is that who you were
on the phone with yesterday?
[SUBARU]
Right.
If I say "yes," then I get
to play ball professionally.
[EMA]
That's really great.
[SUBARU]
Yes and no.
You see, the offer's
from a team in Kyushu.
I definitely wanna be a pro.
Just not so far away.
'Cause I'd never see you!
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
I'd ask you to come with me.
But I know you have entrance
exams to study for.
Um, I think you need
to focus on what's best
for your professional career
and not worry about me.
I don't want you
to quit basketball
and I don't think
you do either.
Playing basketball makes
you happy, right?
So, play it.
[gasps]
I shouldn't have anything
to do with your decision.
Okay.
I appreciate you being
honest with me about this.
Means a lot.
And I guess I have some
things to think about.
Thanks.
[MASAOMI] We'll have
breakfast just as soon
as Subaru gets back.
[EMA]
Kay. Sounds good.
I'll put something
together, then.
[MASAOMI]
Thank you. By the way.
There's somewhere special
we'd like to take you
on our way back home.
Is that all right?
Sure.
Here we are, then.
This is where your real
parents are buried.
[gasps]
We found out
from Rintaro recently.
We asked him about it.
'Cause I guess, we wanted
to pay our respects, too.
[whimpers]
[EMA] Mom, Dad,
I just want you to know.
I have some truly
wonderful brothers now.
And Rintaro-- No, Dad...
Dad and Miss Miwa and
all of my new brothers.
Well, I guess they're
my family now.
So anyway, Mom, Dad.
Thank you for
choosing to have me.
Because I'm so happy.
Hey, are you working?
No way. Having fun.
[WATARU]
Whoa! What's this?
Take a look.
The title I've chosen
is "Brothers' Conflict".
You must know all about that.
Yeah, I guess.
I do have a whole
lotta brothers.
Indeed. So, tell me,
out of these options,
who do you think will win?
Uh...
E. G. O.
[HIKARU]
Right.
[WATARU]
I don't really understand
what this means, but...
Ooh. This one!
What made you pick that one?
'Cause number 13 is the biggest,
which means it has the
biggest attack power!
Uh, well, you're right
about it being
the biggest number of the bunch.
I'm right? Seriously? I knew it!
Dear.
These numbers are odds,
not attack power, got it?
[WATARU]
Odds. Not attacks.
Hey! It's no fair!
Don't just keep giving
her all the games!
Give me some, too, okay?
[NATSUME]
Just so I understand what
you're complaining about here,
what kind of games
do you want, Wataru?
[WATARU]
Games we can all play together!
Sis would love that,
I just know it!
Don'cha think that'd be fun?
[NATSUME]
Hell no!