[romantic music plays]
[SUBARU] Since we met, I can't
stop thinking about you.
[YUSUKE] We can see
each other whenever we want.
[FUTO] You didn't seem like
all the other girls, to me.
[YUSUKE] It's complicated.
I know I shouldn't
have these feelings.
[SUBARU, YUSUKE, FUTO]
But I love you anyway. Forever.
[EMA gasps]
[EMA] Of course you do.
After all, we're family,
aren't we?
[EMA] My dad is getting
remarried and I decided to
live with my new stepbrothers
so he can have some privacy.
Living with twelve boys
definitely ensures
some surprises along the way.
But still, I'm happy
to have so many brothers.
[EMA] I hope that one day
we can all live together,
like a real family.
[JULI] Right! One more day
of fighting off
the horn dog boys
in this house,
so keep your wits about you.
Don't let your
guard down, m'girl!
[EMA] I keep telling you,
they're not horn dogs,
and there's no fight.
Those boys are
my stepbrothers, now.
[EMA]
Oh, hey, good morning!
Good morning to you.
Were you able to
sleep okay last night?
Yes. Thank you
for asking. Wow.
[EMA] Did you make
all this yourself, Ukyo?
[UKYO] I did,
but I tend to be the one
in charge of all the cooking.
[JULI sniffing]
Yum. A classic Japanese
breakfast I see.
Um. Can I help you
out with anything?
[UKYO] Sure. Do you mind
dishing up the rice for me?
We have a lot of
late-risers this morning,
so I think, maybe we only
need to get four places ready.
Okay.
Morning, Sis. How you doing?
Very well.
Thanks for asking.
You're welcome. I'm so
happy. This is the best!
You get to have breakfast
with us from now on, right?
Yup. Lucky me!
[EMA] Morning, guys.
Yeah.
Um. Good morning, Subaru.
Hey.
Well, this is a rare sight.
Yusuke got up in time
to eat breakfast!
[grunts]
[JULI hissing]
Does he have rabies?
[EMA] Oh, Juli.
[EMA] I'm sorry about
how Juli's been acting.
He's not used to being
around guys, so he's anxious.
I get it. How about you?
[EMA] Huh?
I mean, you suddenly have
a bunch of brothers.
That's gotta make you
a little anxious, too.
I guess it is
weird for me in a way.
But everyone
is being really cool.
I mean, you're worried
about me, and that feels nice.
Huh? Don't be stupid.
Just making conversation.
[KISHIDA]
"Which was the beginning
of this modest record.
He had just completed..."
[YUSUKE] She's the
first girl I've ever
seriously had a thing for.
Why did she have to wind up
becoming my stepsister?
I can't accept this.
I will never accept this!
I won't give up on her!
[gasps]
[STUDENTS] Huh?
[EMA] Hello? I'm home!
[EMA] That's strange.
No one's here.
[JULI sniffing]
Someone's here.
I can smell the creep.
He must be Futo Asakura?
Futo's the twelfth son, yeah?
Pop star or what not?
[EMA gasps]
Who the hell are you?
One of my brother's
girlfriends?
What? No!
[FUTO] I don't know how you
managed to get in to my house,
but surely you didn't
actually think you'd get away
with breaking and entering?
No, I... I can't be
breaking and entering
if I live in this house, too.
[FUTO] So, you're
the daughter of the man
my mother's marrying.
[EMA] Yes. That's right.
[FUTO]
Huh. I didn't expect you.
[gasps]
I guess you're cute
in your own way,
but you don't look
terribly clever to me.
[EMA, JULI gasp]
[FUTO]
You're an idiot, aren't you?
Wow. Um, I don't think so.
But if you're an idiot,
how would you know?
I mean,
unless someone told you.
[FUTO] Nice to meet you.
P.S., you're a total idiot.
What was that guy's problem?
He's a completely
twisted jerk-face!
I have to say,
he was definitely different
from the Futo Asakura
I've seen on television.
But I think I might've caught
him a little off guard, too.
[EMA] It's gotta be strange
to wake up to someone
you don't know
walking around your house.
Oh, like any
of that is your fault!
I know. But I still
want to be careful
to stay out of everyone's way
and not be a bother to them.
[EMA]
Welcome back home!
You okay? Something wrong?
Oh, no,
please excuse me. Heh.
It's just been a long time
since someone's said
"welcome home" to me.
It was nice to hear.
[UKYO] That reminds me.
Futo's here.
Have you seen him yet?
[EMA]
Oh. Yeah. We just met.
I hope he was polite.
[UKYO] I seriously doubt he'll
be able to be here tomorrow
with his work and everything,
so I told him to at least
be sure he found time
to come home today.
What's tomorrow?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I haven't told you
about it yet, have I?
It should be fun.
I'm planning on having
a small birthday party
for Subaru.
Wow, a birthday party,
for real?
It's so sweet of you
to do that for him!
We don't normally make such
a big fuss over each other,
but Subaru is
going to turn twenty,
so this year is
a special one for him.
If there's anything
I can do to help you out
with getting ready for
the party, please let me know.
Oh. In that case.
[chuckles]
Are you all right
down there, Chii?
I'm okay, just a little antsy.
I've been put in charge of
making Subaru's birthday cake,
so I'm kind of nervous
I might mess it up.
And jeez,
these bags are way heavy!
I bet Subaru
would be able to carry
all this stuff
with, like, no problem.
Yeah. Gotta give him that.
He does look strong.
He does roadwork every day
on top of training
with the basketball team.
It's really amazing.
I didn't realize
she'd noticed.
Huh?
[JULI] Is something
the matter, Chii?
I thought I heard someone
over there a second ago.
[SUBARU]
What am I even hiding for?
[EMA exhales deeply]
[EMA gasps]
[EMA] Louis?
Louis, are you okay?
[JULI]
You think maybe he's sick?
How're you, Chii?
[EMA] That's weird.
Juli's the only one
who's ever
called me Chii before.
Thinking what I am?
That that is
really, really weird?
[EMA]
Um, are you all right?
[LOUIS]
Yeah. I'm just silly.
I was aiming to
sleep on the sofa,
but I didn't quite make it.
[EMA] Are you done
with work for the day?
[LOUIS] Nope.
Uh. I kinda came back
for you. Or your hair.
[EMA] Huh?
You know, today is
Subaru's birthday after all,
and there's the party.
[LOUIS] I thought I could,
uh, make you look cute.
[EMA gasps]
What? This guy came back
just for that?
[EMA] He's amazing.
He really is.
I don't know why, but I feel
so comfortable and relaxed.
[LOUIS] Almost done.
Well? Do you like it?
Oh yes! I love it!
Well, in that case.
Time for the big finish!
Crap. I think it's broken.
[EMA] Oh no.
[LOUIS] Sorry,
I'll go get another one.
No, please don't!
This is more than
enough already.
It's been fun.
Let me finish.
He just wants to make
sure the job's done right.
He's a professional.
I suppose there are
times when it's
actually worse
to decline a favor.
[JULI] Hm?
Hey you. Where's Louis?
[EMA] Oh, he just stepped away.
He'll be right back.
Oh, great--
you've gotta be kidding!
I asked the salon, and they
said he'd be right here!
[EMA] He was--
are you in a hurry?
Yeah, I don't think so.
Like I'm gonna
tell some random girl
my personal information.
[EMA gasps]
What's different?
It's your hair, right?
--[EMA] Uh...
--[FUTO] Sorry.
[FUTO] I didn't realize
something had changed until
just now. I mean who
knew you'd wind up
being such a
beautiful girl, am I right?
[EMA] Beautiful?
[FUTO] Hey, so uh...
Yeah, what is it?
Just for right now.
Do you mind if,
well, I forget that
you're my stepsister?
Just kidding.
You should have
seen your face.
You thought I was serious.
Did you think
changing your hairstyle
would make you a princess?
--[FUTO laughing]
--[EMA] He's just teasing me.
[cell phone ringing]
Hey, what's up?
Yeah, I'm at home.
Like I already told you,
that studio's hair and
make-up department has like,
no sense of style.
My big brother Louis
is so much better.
[FUTO]
Okay, fine, I'm coming.
[FUTO sighs]
Man, it totally sucks that
Louis isn't here
to help me out.
[FUTO]
See you around, step-sis,
you pretty,
pretty princess you.
Oh wow!
The cake is so big!
It looks delicious!
You just get better
and better, little lady.
It is beautifully made.
That's the truth.
Almost looks too good to eat.
Wow. Thank you all very much.
It's awesome!
It's the most amazing cake
I've ever seen, ever!
Now, Wataru. Try to
remember that Sis made this
especially for Subaru,
so you should let him
be more excited
about it than you are
and try not to get upset
when he gets the first piece.
Understand?
Yeah, I get it.
[WATARU] I'm sorry
about that, Subaru.
That's so sweet.
What a good brother.
[SUBARU gasps, exhales]
[YUSUKE] Hold on. You mean
you made this all by yourself?
[EMA] That's right.
And you made it for Subaru?
Like just for him?
[EMA] Huh?
Well, great. I can't eat it.
[EMA] What? Why not?
It's for everyone to eat.
No, that's not
what this is about.
You took the effort
to make it,
and I feel guilty
about not eating it.
I want to, but somehow.
I just can't.
[EMA]
You don't have to.
Oh, yeah? So you're not
going to have any, Yusuke?
Awesome, I don't mind eating
your share of cake, then.
--[YUSUKE] What?
--[TSUBAKI] We are talking
about a cake that's full of
your love, after all.
I'll eat every
last crumb, I swear!
Hey! What are you
trying to prove here?
Wait! I know!
I'm sure it would be
so much tastier,
and friendlier,
if you fed it to me.
Right? Come on, do it!
[EMA] I don't know.
Would you
rather me feed you.
I'd be perfectly fine
with that as well.
[TSUBAKI]
Let's start with a berry.
Here, now say "ah" for me.
Um.
[AZUSA] Cut it out, Tsubaki.
That's enough of that.
Yes, sir.
But I gotta say, it looks
like the birthday boy
in question over there
is in no state to enjoy it.
Oh no.
[EMA]
Is something wrong?
Don't worry about him.
It's not like
he's sick, exactly.
Well, it's a kind of illness.
[EMA] What?
The kind there's no
cure for, but, you know,
I suffer from
the same aching, too.
[EMA gasps]
And if it's at all possible,
I'd prefer to have
this particular illness
for the rest of my life.
Oh. I don't uh.
[IORI] You know
you're embarrassing her.
Cut it out, Kaname.
My sincerest apologies.
No. It's okay.
Hey, do you mind if
I ask you something?
No, no, ask away.
Okay. Why did you
change your hairstyle?
Oh. I didn't do this.
Louis offered
to change it for me.
He said it was for the party.
Yeah, that does make sense.
Well, it looks
really good on you.
Thanks.
That's nice of you to say.
[UKYO]
I think it's about time.
Subaru, blow out your candles.
[SUBARU]
You're serious about this?
Yep.
[SUBARU sighs]
[EMA] I'll take pictures
for you guys.
[inhales]
[SUBARU blows]
--[laughing, clapping]
--[UKYO] Happy birthday!
[WATARU] It's delicious!
Your cake is the best in
the whole wide world, Big Sis!
I completely agree!
Are you sure
you don't want any?
Because if you're not
eating any of this magic,
then I'll take it.
Back off!
This is good cake!
[ALL laugh]
[YUSUKE] I'm serious!
[camera clicks]
[EMA]
I hope you like it okay.
Thanks. Um.
It's really tasty.
Isn't that cute.
He likes what you made.
Yeah.
[EMA]  Oh good.
I'm so relieved
they all liked my cake.
[EMA] Having a lot
of family is so cool.
Well, if you ask me,
this house is too rowdy.
True, but it's still fun.
You know, like throwing
birthday parties for each other.
It's just neat.
Compared to your dad, yeah.
Rintaro was working
overseas for almost
all of your birthdays.
He sent postcards and things.
He may not have been here,
but I have lots of
good memories with Dad.
[EMA] Living in a crazy
house like this, though,
it's exciting!
Oh? Where's my phone?
Did you forget and
leave it in the living room?
[TSUBAKI] Man, I would've killed
for her to make me a cake.
[SUBARU'S cell phone ringing]
[AZUSA] It was good.
She's got a gift.
[NATSUME]
Happy birthday, kiddo.
Turning twenty
is a pivotal year.
It's time to really
start stepping up
your game on the court.
Make sure you don't get
preoccupied with anything else.
Keep it together.
[SUBARU] Arrogant bastard.
Is something wrong?
Spill it, my beloved brother.
Beloved brother, my ass.
Quit being so stupid.
You don't mean that.
I know what the problem is.
You're having a hard time
keeping your mind off
a certain someone.
What? That's not true,
so shut your mouth!
[TSUBAKI] Don't be so dramatic.
Our new little sis.
I wanna know what
you think about her.
What do I think about her?
Too embarrassed to say?
That proves it.
I knew that
she was on your mind!
You are so far off, man!
Oh yeah? Then why
are you so distracted?
[SUBARU]
It's, you know, like...
To be honest,
that girl is a pain in my ass!
[EMA gasps]
[SUBARU] It's been just
us guys for all this time,
and suddenly this chick
shows up out of nowhere.
And... it's like, now I
can't even act like normal.
[SUBARU]
I mean, what if I wanna
walk around the house naked?
[EMA] I had no idea.
Anyway,
I gotta hit the head.
[gasps]
[EMA] I'm sorry.
Uh...!
[EMA] He's right, you know.
I really have been in the way.
That jerk! What kind of
bastard makes a girl cry?
No, it's okay.
I'm not even crying.
[JULI] Whatever!
You're crying on the inside!
I can tell! Man,
you always get all forgive-y
when you're hurt. I hate that!
--[EMA] Juli.
--[door bell rings]
[gasps]
[SUBARU] I'm sorry.
I was wrong to say that.
Please, just forget it.
It was the heat of the moment,
and I didn't mean to uh...
I'm an idiot, okay?
Oh. It's all right.
I was just taken
aback a little bit.
Look, I--!
Hey. I really am okay.
I'm sorry.
I really am very sorry.
--[SUBARU groans]
--[EMA gasps]
[thud]
[JULI squeaks angrily]
[groans]
[EMA] Hm?!
--Hey!
--What are you two doing?
[TSUBAKI]
Why you little scamp!
[TSUBAKI sighs]
Look at him.
He's completely zonked out.
[AZUSA] Must have had
too much to drink.
[TSUBAKI]
Man, he's hopeless, isn't he?
Hey, by the way.
Just forget what
Subaru was saying.
We're glad you're here,
and so is Subaru.
No matter what he said.
I was kinda
giving him a hard time
and he was just trying
to get me to shut up.
I'm sorry about that.
Oh, sure.
But how did this
end up happening?
Did little Subaru
make a move on you?
Uh! That's not it.
He just tripped and
fell on me, that's all.
[AZUSA] So you're saying
it was an accident?
Yes. Exactly.
[AZUSA] If you say so.
Well, whether it was
on purpose or wasn't,
I hope he doesn't think
that tonight is just
gonna be forgotten.
'Cause that ain't happening.
[JULI] Huh?
[birds chirping]
[TSUBAKI] Morning!
Sorry about yesterday.
Here. You'd forgotten
your cell phone, remember?
[EMA] Oh. Yeah, thanks.
[TSUBAKI] Also, we made sure
to get Subaru back for you,
so you don't have to
worry about him anymore.
[EMA] What?
It might have been
a little over the top,
but oh well, he brought
all that on himself.
[EMA]
So um, I don't understand.
Did you do something to him?
[TSUBAKI] Yeah but, uh...
it's not for delicate eyes,
so you shouldn't see it.
[AZUSA] I definitely agree.
[EMA] Mm.
[UKYO]
Good morning, everyone.
[EMA] Hi.
And good morning to you!
Are you hanging
those out to dry?
[UKYO] Yes, actually
if you don't mind,
I'd appreciate it
if you'd take over.
Sure!
[EMA] Being asked to do
chores makes me feel like
a part of the family.
Who would have guessed housework
would make me so happy?
Ukyo, the pseudo-mom,
seems to be quite
the perceptive guy
for a lawyer,
wouldn't you say?
Still though!
You need to watch out
for that ninth
brat-face, Subaru!
[EMA] Yes, yes.
Thanks for worrying.
I really do appreciate it.
But I'll keep hoping,
maybe one day soon,
Subaru will find a way
to finally accept me as
a part of the family, too.
[SUBARU grunts]
Get it together,
Asahina!
Sorry, coach!
Damn.
What's going on with me?
Why can't I focus?
This one looks good.
[EMA] Oh? Hey there, Futo!
[FUTO grunts]
Don't call out my name
in a loud voice,
you simple twit!
--Huh?
--Say what?
How dare you
say that to my Chii?
What am I gonna do
if the other customers
figure out I'm here?
Oh, yes, that's right.
I'm sorry.
[FUTO]
Let's go. Seriously.
[EMA] Wow. Are you
renting all of those?
It's research for a gig.
Really, Futo.
You're going to be in a movie?
[FUTO] Will you shut up?
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL 2A]
Oh my god, it's totally him!
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL 2B]
What? No way!
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL 2C]
I heard that he lives...
Well, great. Now I can't
take my time browsing
because of your loud mouth.
Oh, that's too bad.
Yeah, just take
responsibility and
rent these for me.
I'll be waiting at home.
[JULI hissing]
Oh. Have you been waiting?
You're late! How long
were you planning to
keep me waiting
for some stupid DVDs?
I really am
sorry about this.
An apology won't
get you off the hook.
Don't fool yourself, princess.
As punishment, you'll
have to do all sorts of things.
Most of them in your room.
[EMA gasps]
[TSUBAKI] Azusa, have you
decided what song
we're gonna
sing at the wedding?
[AZUSA] Are you really
gonna make me sing too?
Yeah, of course.
Who else can I find
to harmonize perfectly
with me other than you?
[cell phones ringing]
[BOTH gasp]
Well, that's a surprise.
So he's coming after all.
We haven't seen him
in what seems like forever.
It'll be his first time
meeting her, too!
I hope nothing too awkward
happens with her there.
Now, why do you look like
you're up to something?
Hey, I can't help but
imagine what might go down
when he comes
face-to-face with Subaru.
[AZUSA] I'm guessing there's
more to it than that.
[MASAOMI] So Subaru,
what do you want
for your twentieth
birthday present?
[SUBARU] I don't
care about that stuff.
[MASAOMI]
I figured you'd say that.
So, here, say, "Ah."
Come on, don't be shy.
[SUBARU] Masaomi, can this be
the last checkup for a while?
The lollypop's not worth it.