[romantic music plays]
[TSUBAKI] I've been thinking
of you as my little sister.
[AZUSA] We live together
and see each other every day.
[TSUBAKI] But I have to admit
those feelings have changed.
[AZUSA] It's not easy
telling you how I really feel.
[AZUSA, TSUBAKI] I love you.
[AZUSA, TSUBAKI] Forever.
[EMA] Of course
we love each other.
We're family.
[upbeat music plays]
[EMA] Finally. I get to
meet my new family today.
I can't believe
I have brothers, now.
I hope they like me.
[JULI] Saw that! A look of
complete lack of cynicism!
Chii, thirteen males require
suspicion at all times!
[EMA] I know, Juli.
That's all you've talked about
since you found out
I was moving.
[JULI] I mean what in
pie's name were Rintaro
and this new mother
of yours thinking?
Throw you to a barn
full of hungry males
while they move into
a new house together?
It doesn't make sense!
[EMA] Sure it does. Dad and
Miss Miwa are newlyweds.
They want a life of their own.
It's what people do.
Plus, they're both
too busy with work.
[JULI] Sure.
Now putting you in danger
seems like a great idea!
[EMA] Juli. You do realize
these people you think
are so dangerous
are my brothers now, right?
They're not
some random strangers.
[JULI] They're still boys
bursting with hormones
I can't pronounce!
And if they even
look at you funny,
those brothers are going down!
We're almost there.
Yes! Take me
to the battlefield!
[EMA sighs]
Oh, they're already here.
[JULI] Uh! Whoa!
[EMA] Excuse me! Hi.
[MASAOMI] Hi. You must
be our new sister!
They're taking your
things up to your room.
Oh. Thanks.
My name's Masaomi,
and I'm the oldest.
And this one's
the youngest. Wataru.
Hey there!
What up, Big Sis?
Uh. Hey yourself.
Thanks for having me.
I'm glad to be here.
Well good, we're glad
that you're here, too.
Oh. These two aren't the pervy
scumballs I was expecting.
But just you wait!
[JULI] Brace yourself, kiddo.
We're moving into
a battlefield, here.
I better fuel up
before the others return.
And... as long as
we're in this house,
you don't leave my side.
[JULI] You got that?
[crunching]
It's not safe.
The fight of our lives
is ahead of us!
All for one and--! Crap.
[JULI] Chii! Where did you go?
[JULI] Chii!
[JULI grunts]
I'm coming for you, Chii!
Follow my voice!
[SUBARU gasps]
[KANAME] What is it?
Someone out there?
[SUBARU] Maybe? Weird.
Ready to die, kid?
Oh, you must be Subaru,
the ninth son, huh?
[JULI] Ah! No pinching!
[SUBARU] Whoa.
[KANAME]
It's a little squirrel.
Hey there, buddy.
Where'd you come from?
Are you lost?
[yells] Kaname.
Brother number three, I presume.
You're making
my tie uneven! Let go!
[KANAME] Owie.
[SUBARU] Why are you
bringing it with us?
[KANAME] You never know.
This could be someone's pet.
I don't want it
to get hurt out there.
I know exactly who you are.
You play basketball
and think we should all
worship you because of it.
Rintaro goes on and on
about you like you're
some kind of miracle whip.
But I ain't fooled.
I smell your nasty mind funk!
[JULI] It's full of
kink and smut and mess!
You keep away from Chii,
you hear me?
[JULI sqeaking angrily]
So yeah. Why does it seem like
this squirrel hates us?
It doesn't. I just
think he's excited.
[ding dong]
[KANAME] Iori? Hey.
You're back early today.
Early but not by my doing.
Ukyo told me to come home.
[JULI]
Hmph! So that's Iori?
The smart popular one
who's good at sports.
Hm?
[ding dong]
I gotta go change but
I'll be there in a bit.
[IORI] 'Kay.
These all going to the kitchen?
Yeah. Can you
grab some for me?
Sure. What is that?
It's a squirrel.
[ding dong]
[SUBARU]
Whoa! It's running away.
This is not "running away!"
This is "being the hero!"
Oh. Hello there.
Hark! I hear a voice.
I'm coming, Chii!
[EMA gasps]
Give us a welcome home hug.
[TSUBAKI]
It's, nice to meet you, Sis.
[screams]
Unhand her!
[TSUBAKI] Ah!
I'm sorry you had to
see that. My name's Azusa.
Good to have you here.
Ow. That hurt.
Freaky, isn't it?
Tsubaki and I
are identical twins.
All right you two.
Let's not intimidate her.
[UKYO] Good to meet you.
My name's Ukyo.
I'm the attorney of the family.
[JULI squeaks]
Oh, so you're
a high-end bastard!
They keep getting
better and better!
[JULI squeaks angrily]
Cool. It's nice to
meet you, too.
Wow. You're so pretty.
[hisses]
[YUSUKE] Tsubaki!
Thought I told you not to
bring your game in the house!
[TSUBAKI] Well!
Look who decided to show up!
Yeah! I live here!
And I don't want to have to
watch your make out sessions!
--[YUSUKE gasps]
--[EMA] Uh.
No way?
Yusuke, hi.
Why are you here?
Um. Because I--.
Tsubaki. I suppose
this means you
didn't inform Yusuke
like I asked you?
Why? Wait, let me guess.
You forgot?
You know, your tone sounds
extremely judgey right now.
Look. I did not
sign up for this mess.
[YUSUKE] You're my classmate.
Not my sister. Got it?
[TSUBAKI] Seriously? Why are
you being so dramatic, bro?
You can't just disown her.
[YUSUKE]
Wrong, I do what I want!
[EMA]
Yusuke Asahina, of course.
I should've just
known by his last name.
[YUSUKE]
No, no! Get off of me!
[JULI]
So. How you holding up, kid?
Do we need to
go to the hospital?
Your face looks weird!
No. I'm okay. Really.
And at last we meet.
You look lovely.
If you're ever in the mood for
a riveting Buddhist sermon,
I would be delighted
to give you one, my dear.
Kaname, that's gross!
Hey! I remember you!
[JULI squeaks]
--[KANAME] Mmm!
--[EMA gasps]
Is it too cold in here?
Do you want me
to turn the air down?
Oh. No. It's all right.
[KANAME] No it's not.
In fact, it's a little stuffy.
Compression of
body heat does that.
Right. Yes.
Um, I'm sorry about
Juli hurting you earlier.
Please, don't worry about it.
I can't be mad at him for
trying to make new friends.
Soon it'll be like
he's my pet, too.
[EMA] Sure.
[squeaks angrily]
[chuckles]
[EMA] I'm so sorry.
[JULI] Watch yourself!
This place is lousy
with dopes, isn't it?
[IORI] Were you shocked?
I mean, that there
are so many of us?
[EMA] Yeah.
I knew about all of you,
but I'm still
kinda overwhelmed.
[WATARU] It's gonna be super
cool to have a big sister!
Hey! Do you wanna
see a giant bunny?
There's one in my room!
Come on! I'll show you!
[MASAOMI] Not now, Wataru.
She just got here.
Aw...
[KANAME] All in good time.
And this still isn't all of us
if you can believe it.
One is at work,
two don't live here,
and then there's
this guy. Watch.
[singing]
[WATARU]
Look, it's Futo!
[EMA] That's Futo?
That fake smile
looks like a cry for help.
[chuckles]
He's on tour.
I was wondering
where he went.
I knew I hadn't
seen him around.
Last thing I heard
he was in Hokkaido.
Have you ever been there?
We'll ask him to bring you
a souvenir if you want.
Thanks. That'd be nice.
Futo is our little
rockstar brother.
All his fans know him
as Asakura, though.
Can you believe that
he's this famous already?
At fifteen?
[gasps]
That's amazing.
[FUTO singing]
[EMA] But I can believe it.
I bet with this many brothers
he needed a way to stand out.
And his dad was gone a lot,
just like mine.
That always made me
want to travel.
He probably likes
being on tour so much.
Funny how I feel like
I understand him.
[EMA gasps]
[EMA] They seem nice.
I hope they stay that way.
[dinging]
[EMA] Oh my? Why does
everything look blurry?
[MASAOMI]
Are you feeling okay?
I'm great.
Just got a little dizzy.
[JULI] Chii?
[EMA gasps]
[AZUSA, TSUBAKI, SUBARU gasp]
[MASAOMI]
You don't look that great.
You're really burning up.
[yells]
I'm so sorry. I didn't
mean to scare anyone.
I really am feeling better.
Are you mad at me?
[KANAME] Of course not!
There's no need to apologize.
And, fortunately, we have a
trained doctor in the house!
I'm just a
pediatrician actually,
but I can help with
whatever you may need.
Thank you. That's very kind.
Wow, that must
be a really cool job.
Yeah too bad
he sucks at it.
Did he even think to mention
that it might be exhaustion?
After you were packing all day
with no food or sleep?
[door opens]
[LOUIS] Don't you hate that?
[BOTH gasp]
[UKYO] Louis. I didn't
realize you were home.
Yeah. I heard people...
like, talking and stuff, so...
I told you about Louis.
Not sure if you remember.
Number eight.
Oh. Nice to meet you.
Sorry about not
getting up. I feel rude.
Don't sweat it, Chii.
It's been a long day.
What?
[LOUIS] Setting sail
to a whole new world,
and now being surrounded
by the natives
and learning their language.
I bet that would
knock anyone out.
It's not that bad.
Stop the car.
Did Hipster Boy
just call you Chii?
Your hair. Wow. So like,
when you're better,
I'll have to give you
a little... makeover.
[EMA] Huh...?
[UKYO] Oh. Louis is
a wonderful hairstylist.
Yeah, thanks. That'd be fun.
Hm.
How are you doing sitting up?
Any dizziness now?
[EMA] Actually, no. I think
the medicine is working.
Great.
She should still take
it easy for a little while.
Maybe some nice
rice soup for dinner?
Sure. Sound okay?
Sounds perfect.
[UKYO] Oh, by the way,
the plumbing down here
needs repairing. So, when you
go to take a bath later,
use the one on
the fifth floor. Cool?
Have you been up there?
I don't think so.
But there's a layout
of the place on her desk.
[EMA] Oh. Thanks.
[MASAOMI]
Don't stay up there too long.
Goodnight and
sweet dreams, Sis.
[exhales deeply]
[JULI]
Earth to Chii! Do you copy?
It's been such a long time
since anyone's been around
to tell me goodnight.
[EMA] Feels like I have
family now. It's nice.
[JULI] Hm?
[TSUBAKI] Hurry up!
You've been in there forever!
[AZUSA] It may have been
three minutes tops!
You can wait five more.
[YUSUKE]
Get out! It's not a chapel!
[KANAME] Excuse me?
[YUSUKE] "Porcelain God"
is an expression.
You don't actually
pray in there!
--[KANAME] What?
--[TSUBAKI] I'm coming in!
I guess this is
the norm now.
Living here sure
will be interesting
with all these boys.
[YOUNG EMA breathing heavily]
[JULI] Look, I get that
growing up you had to do
a lot of things on your own.
Match Girl style.
And now it feels warm
and fuzzy-like to have
more family around
to help take care of you.
But let's get
one thing straight.
Remember me? I was
your family first, Chii.
Don't you forget. I'm always
gonna have your back.
I know.
[EMA exhales]
[KANAME]
Sorry. Did I wake you?
[EMA gasps] Oh. No.
[KANAME] Good. Just a little
gift from all of us.
Wow. Thanks, Kaname.
That's sweet.
Why don't you
call me brother?
[EMA gasps]
Brother, right.
Sounds lovely from your lips.
Please, say it for me again.
Um. Brother?
[KANAME chuckles]
[JULI] Kitty litter. Trees.
Are you sleepy yet?
[EMA]
I'm getting there. Thanks.
Will it help if your
big brother sleeps next to you?
[EMA] I don't think so.
Aww. Well. That's too bad.
If you get scared or
need anything, let me know.
I'm always
here for you, Baby Sis.
Thank you.
That means a lot to me.
[KANAME] Me too.
Have a good night, my dear.
[JULI] I saw that!
[EMA] For a second I thought
you were going to kiss me.
[JULI] Mm?
[KANAME] I'm sorry.
But you never know.
Maybe I'll do that someday.
Now I know for sure
you're just teasing me.
[KANAME] Uh.
I mean you are,
aren't you, Kaname?
Sorry, I'm still so fuzzy.
[KANAME] Get some rest.
We don't need your temperature
raising any higher.
I couldn't handle being
responsible for that.
[KANAME] We'll talk again
once you're well.
[KANAME]
And I promise next time...
the kiss won't be
at all confusing.
[EMA quavered exhale]
[pleased exhale]
[Come on, toothbrush.
I know you're in here.
Are you really gonna
take a bath right now?
It's kinda late, isn't it?
Yeah. I already got
a little bit of sleep,
and I think it would
help relax me.
[JULI] Well you're
not going by yourself!
I call "Bath Chaperone!"
But why?
I'm just going upstairs?
[EMA] Guess it's left.
[JULI grunts]
[EMA]
What are you doing, silly?
You never know what's around
the corners in this place.
The toilet's over there.
So, then.
The bath is that way.
Hey what's up?
[EMA gasps]
Is everything all right?
Um. Yeah. I'm sorry.
[EMA] Uh...!
[SUBARU] Oh, my bad!
[EMA] No. Uh...
[EMA] Sorry to bother you!
[EMA sighs]
That was so awkward.
What did I say?
You shouldn't be living here
with a bunch of random guys!
[TSUBAKI] Listen.
There's something I've wanted
to tell you for a while.
[JULI] Who dat?
[TSUBAKI] This is hard.
We've been together
for so long now.
Naturally.
But lately. I don't know,
I can't explain it.
[TSUBAKI]
Something's changed.
You lost?
[EMA gasps]
[TSUBAKI]
When I'm with you,
my heart races and
my palms start sweating.
Also, I don't really know why,
but I get so upset
when you're with other guys.
[AZUSA] What?
I... I think I love you.
[TSUBAKI]
And I want you to be mine.
[JULI] Whaddaya know?
Could have told you
they swung that way.
Well yeah,
but they're... brothers.
So they couldn't really be--
Hey, what do you
think you heard?
[EMA] I forgot
something in my room!
Uh. Bye.
[TSUBAKI] Someone up here?
What's going on?
[AZUSA]
How are you feeling?
[EMA] Uh. I'm good.
Oh dear. Your face
still looks flushed.
Careful, could be a fever.
No. I'm fine, really.
Uh... Is there something
you want to talk about?
No. I'm just tired.
[TSUBAKI] I know what it is.
Sleeping in a
new place is rough.
If you're scared,
you can sleep in my bed, eh?
--[EMA] I'm not.
--[SUBARU] Tsubaki, come on.
You can talk to
us about anything.
That's what big
brothers are for, right?
Um. Yeah...
[JULI] Chii!
You might as well tell them
what you heard earlier.
No reason to be cagey if they're
gonna be so open about it.
Fine! You have my
support no matter what!
We're family and I love you.
Thanks, I feel better now.
Uh. Good? But uh...
Yeah. I may have
overheard, uh, your,
your conversation earlier.
Conversation? The one we
just had downstairs?
Ah. It all makes sense now.
The time was right.
I'd been suppressing
my feelings for so long.
I finally had to tell Azusa
I'm in love with him.
Uh. You're what?
I hope you're not mad at me.
[TSUBAKI] Of course not!
It's about time
we came out with the truth.
Right, Pussycat?
[AZUSA clears throat]
Okay, that's enough.
[EMA] I'm happy
for you both! Goodnight!
[TSUBAKI laughing]
You guys are hysterical!
Best reactions ever!
[EMA] Huh?
[AZUSA] Tsubaki's a jerk.
We were just doing
a read-through of a script.
[EMA] A script?
[TSUBAKI] Yep.
I always like to
rehearse before our gigs.
[EMA] It wasn't real?
No. These two jerks
are voice actors.
You were acting.
I thought you were freaks.
My bad, fellas!
[EMA gasps]
Oh, please forgive me.
I interrupted your rehearsal!
I'm so sorry!
It's cool.
We're over it! But...
I would love to have a female
reader if you're interested?
It would really help me
with my character.
Oh stop. Don't you think
she's had enough
of that tonight?
[TSUBAKI laughs]
Yeah, I guess so.
You're still
on the mend, right?
Hm.
Sorry about that.
They're weird.
We've all thrown
a lot at you today.
It's... fine.
[EMA sighs]
Feels like my heart's gonna
burst out of my chest.
[JULI] Finally!
It's about time you laid down.
I'll stay here and keep an eye
on you till you fall asleep.
Thanks, Juli.
I'm glad you're here.
Where am I exactly?
[EMA] It's like we've discovered
a bizarre new universe.
[YUSUKE]
Crap! Why is this happening?
Why did it have to be
her of all people?
[UKYO] Pink? Actually no.
That's much too predictable.
[YUSUKE]
What are you talking about?
[UKYO] I'm trying to figure out
which color chopsticks
to set with her rice bowl.
[YUSUKE]
She lives here, you know.
You could just ask her.
Wait, no!
I'll do it! I'll ask her!
[UKYO] What was that about?