[Uragiri no Yuyake
by Theater Brook]
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> I’LL RELY ON NUMBERS!
>> both: IT’S HERE!
>> THIS IS THE DOLLARS?
>> WHAT IS THIS?
THEY CAN’T--
ARE THEY ALL REALLY--
>> FOR STARTERS, YOU COULD MARRY
ME.
>> AFTER ALL, YOU ARE KEEPING
THAT THING A SECRET.
>> CELTY.
>> [chuckles]
THIS IS SO MUCH FUN.
>> DO YOU HEAR ME SCREAMING?
THIS IS MY MOMENT.
THIS IS MY TIME TO BE BORN.
>> I WANT CELTY.
GIVE HER BACK!
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
[running]
[grunting]
>> I HAVE TO THANK YOU FOR WHAT
YOU’VE DONE.
IF IT WEREN’T FOR YOU, I’M
PRETTY SURE MY SISTER WOULD
HAVE JUST LOCKED HER IN THAT
CRAMPED RESEARCH LAB AGAIN.
>> SEIJI.
YOU OKAY?
>> I WANT YOU TO GIVE CELTY
BACK.
SHE AND I HAVE TO GET OUT OF
HERE BEFORE THE COPS ARRIVE.
>> YOU THINK THIS’LL WORK?
IT WON’T!
>> YOU DON’T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
THIS.
I’VE BEEN WATCHING AND ADMIRING
HER EVER SINCE I WAS A LITTLE
KID.
I WANTED TO SET HER FREE.
RELEASE HER INTO THIS GREAT BIG
WORLD WHERE THE TWO OF US WOULD
LIVE TOGETHER FOREVER.
SHE’S ALL I EVER THINK ABOUT.
EVERY DAY, EVERY HOUR, EVERY
MINUTE.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
NO ONE CAN STOP THE POWER OF
LOVE.
BUT ENOUGH ABOUT ME.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
SEEMS LIKE YOU KEEP RELYING ON
NUMBERS TO HELP YOU OUT.
[grunts]
[exclamations]
IT’LL TAKE MORE THAN THAT TO
STOP OUR LOVE!
[grunting]
IT’S NO USE!
PAIN MEANS NOTHING TO ME.
THERE’LL BE NO PAIN IN THE LIFE
I’LL HAVE WITH CELTY.
BEAT ME ALL YOU WANT, I DON’T
CARE.
I WON’T FEEL IT!
>> THAT’S INSANE!
>> NO, DON’T!
PLEASE DON’T HURT HIM!
JUST LISTEN.
I KNOW SEIJI IS HARSH AND
VIOLENT AT TIMES BUT HE’S NOT A
BAD PERSON.
AND THERE’S SOMEONE IN THIS
WORLD HE TRULY LOVES.
>> NO WAY.
NO, THIS CAN’T BE.
THIS CAN’T BE!
>> I DON’T BELIEVE IT. THAT’S...
>> THAT ISN’T MY HEAD!
>> THAT GIRL.
IS HER NAME...
MIKA HARIMA.
>> YOU’RE HER, AREN’T YOU?
THE GIRL THAT SEIJI SUPPOSEDLY
KILLED.
YOU’RE MIKA HARIMA!
>> CAN’T BE.
TELL ME...
HE’S WRONG.
>> I’M SO SORRY!
HELLO, SEIJI.
I KNOW THAT YOU’RE IN THERE.
I’VE COME BACK AGAIN!
OH, NO, YOU FORGOT TO LEAVE THE
DOOR OPEN FOR ME.
I CAN’T COME IN AND SEE YOU.
ARE YOU SLEEPING RIGHT NOW?
O YOU REMEMBER ME?
I’M THE GIRL WHO SAT NEXT TO
YOU DURING THE ENTRANCE EXAM AT
SCHOOL.
TO MY RIGHT WAS SOME KID WITH A
WEIRD LAST NAME LIKE RYUGAMINE.
SO I TURNED TO MY LEFT TO SEE
WHAT THAT PERSON’S LAST NAME
WAS...
AND FELL IN LOVE THE MOMENT I
SAW YOU.
WHEN OUR EYES MET, YOU SMILED
AT ME.
COME ON, SEIJI.
SHOW ME YOUR FACE AGAIN!
PLEASE, PLEASE!
MAYBE YOU’RE NOT FEELING GOOD.
IS THAT WHY YOU CAN’T ANSWER
THE DOOR?
IF THAT’S THE CASE, THEN DON’T
WORRY ABOUT IT.
I’ll OPEN IT....
RIGHT NOW!
[door unlocks]
AFTER WE MET TAKING THE EXAM,
I DID A LITTLE RESEARCH.
I KNOW YOUR BIRTHDAY AND YOUR
FAMILY...
S-SEIJI?
>> YOU SAW IT?
>> YEAH, BUT IT’S OKAY.
I WON’T TELL ANYONE, I PROMISE.
I-I WON’T TELL A SOUL!
WHATEVER YOU’RE INTO, IT’S FINE.
I’M COOL WITH IT!
UM, SO I...
>> IT’S OKAY.
>> SEIJI!
>> SEIJI, ARE YOU...
>> IT’S OKAY.
[grunts]
>> I’M SORRY!
I’M SORRY I DIDN’T DIE!
AND THEN YOUR SISTER...
>> YOU WANT SEIJI TO LOVE YOU,
RIGHT?
GOOD GIRL.
AND THAT’S WHEN THIS DOCTOR
SHOWED UP.
HE SAID THAT, WITH A LITTLE
PLASTIC SURGERY AND SOME MAKEUP,
I COULD LOOK JUST LIKE THE HEAD
THAT YOU’RE IN LOVE WITH.
HE TOLD ME MY NAME WOULD BE
CELTY.
BECAUSE THAT’S WHAT THE HEAD IS
CALLED.
I TRIED, I TRIED HARD TO BE
CELTY FOR YOUR SAKE.
BUT YOUR SISTER SAID IT WASN’T
ENOUGH.
SHE WANTED ME TO START TAKING
DRUGS AND HAVE MORE SURGERY TO
ERASE MY MEMORIES.
BUT I DIDN’T WANT TO DO THAT.
>> A DOCTOR WHO KNOWS MY NAME...
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> WHO KNOWS THAT I’M A
DULLAHAN.
>> SO I RAN AWAY...
>> THERE’S ONLY ONE PERSON LIKE
THAT IN THIS WHOLE CITY!
>> I DID ALL THIS FOR YOU!
SO I COULD BE WITH YOU!
[crowd murmuring]
[horse whinnies]
>> NO, THIS CAN’T BE TRUE.
THIS MEANS THAT...
>> WELL...YOU COULDN’T EVEN TELL
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THE
GENUINE ARTICLE AND THE FAKE.
GUESS YOUR LOVE WASN’T THAT
STRONG AFTER ALL.
SUCKS TO BE YOU.
>> SEIJI!
>> UM, I HAVE TO SAY, THE FACT
THAT YOU WERE WILLING TO RISK
YOUR LIFE TO GET HER BACK IS
PRETTY ADMIRABLE.
AND IT TURNS OUT THAT I WAS
ACTUALLY WRONG ABOUT MIKA.
SOME OF THE THINGS SHE DOES MAY
BE STRANGE BUT...I REALLY
DON’T THINK SHE’S A STALKER.
I MEAN, YOU RISKED YOUR LIFE TO
SAVE SEIJI.
I DON’T THINK SOMEONE WOULD DO
THAT IF THEY WERE ONLY IN IT
FOR THEMSELVES.
AND EVEN THOUGH HE TRIED TO
KILL YOU, YOU STILL LOVED HIM.
THAT’S AMAZING.
IN SOME WAYS.
SO THEN I GUESS...YOU AND
SEIJI...YOU’RE A LOT ALIKE.
[door slams]
[footsteps]
[door opening and shutting]
>> WELCOME HOME.
I’M GUESSING YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHY I DID WHAT I DID.
AND YOUR NEXT QUESTION IS...
"YOU’VE KNOWN ALL ALONG, HAVEN’T
YOU?
THAT MY HEAD WAS IN THEIR LAB?
I BET YOU AND YOUR DAD HAD BEEN
WORKING WITH YAGIRI
PHARMACEUTICALS THIS WHOLE TIME.
AND CHANCES ARE IT WAS YOUR DAD
WHO TOOK MY HEAD FROM ME IN
THE FIRST PLACE!
BUT FOR SOME REASON YOU DECIDED
TO HIDE ALL THAT FROM ME.
AND BUTCHERED SOME POOR,
INNOCENT GIRL’S FACE INSTEAD!
I MAY BE A MONSTER...
BUT THE SAVAGE BEAST WHO REALLY
DESTROYS PEOPLE’S LIVES IS YOU!"
WAS THAT CLOSE?
LOOK, I JUST DON’T WANT THERE
TO BE ANY CONFUSION ON THIS.
I REALLY DON’T KNOW IF MY DAD
STOLE YOUR HEAD OR NOT, AND, TO
BE HONEST, I DON’T CARE.
AND THAT POOR GIRL YOU SPOKE OF
VOLUNTEERED FOR THAT SURGERY,
ALTHOUGH CHANCES ARE YAGIRI DID
PERSUADE HER TO DO IT.
BUT IN THE END, THAT’S NONE OF
MY BUSINESS.
"DO YOU REALLY KNOW WHAT I’M
THINKING?
ARE YOU ACTUALLY READING MY
MIND?" YOU ASK?
YES...OF COURSE I CAN.
I’VE LOVED YOU FOR TWENTY YEARS,
CELTY.
I CAN TELL WHAT YOU’RE THINKING.
>> [gasps]
>> BUT THEN WHY?
IF YOU LOVE ME, WHY DIDN’T YOU
TELL ME WHERE MY HEAD WAS?
>> THAT’S THE REASON.
IT’S BECAUSE I LOVE YOU THAT I
DIDN’T TELL YOU.
IF YOU HAD YOUR HEAD, THEN I’M
AFRAID YOU WOULD LEAVE ME.
AND I KNOW THAT I COULDN’T BEAR
THAT.
EVEN THOUGH I KNEW IT’D MAKE
YOU HAPPY, I COULDN’T TELL YOU.
WE’RE EACH FIGHTING FOR
SOMETHING, AND WHAT’S AT STAKE
ARE OUR HEARTS.
I NEVER WANT TO LOSE YOU.
AND IF I HAVE TO SACRIFICE THE
LIFE AND LOVE OF OTHERS, OR
EVEN MYSELF, THEN SO BE IT.
IT’S HYPOCRITICAL...
BUT IF I HAVE TO USE YOUR
EMOTIONS TOO, I WILL.
>> I DON’T KNOW WHY YOU’D THINK
THAT.
EVEN IF I HAD MY HEAD, I
WOULDN’T LEAVE YOU.
I...
>> THAT MAY BE WHAT YOUR HEART
WANTS, BUT...YOUR HEAD MAY NOT
FEEL THE SAME.
I’VE REALLY THOUGHT ABOUT THIS.
YOU’RE A MYTHICAL FAERIE.
WHY DO YOU CHOOSE TO REVEAL
YOURSELF TO HUMANS AS EASILY AS
YOU DO?
MAYBE SOMEHOW BY LOSING YOUR
HEAD, IT’S ALLOWED YOU TO TAKE
ON MORE OF A PHYSICAL FORM.
AND IF THAT’S TRUE, THEN WHO’S
TO SAY AFTER YOU GET YOUR HEAD
BACK THAT YOU WON’T JUST VANISH
INTO THIN AIR, AS IF ALL OF
THIS WAS NOTHING MORE THAN A
DREAM?
THAT’S MY BIGGEST FEAR.
>> WILL YOU BELIEVE WHAT I’M
ABOUT TO SAY?
>> IF YOU SAY IT’S TRUE, I’LL
BELIEVE YOU.
TO BE HONEST, YOU’RE THE ONLY
ONE I BELIEVE.
>> I’M SCARED TOO.
I’M SCARED OF DYING.
I KNOW THAT IN MY CURRENT
PHYSICAL STATE, NO ONE’S
CAPABLE OF KILLING ME.
THIS ISN’T ME BEING ARROGANT.
IT JUST A STATEMENT OF FACT.
I TAKE NO JOY OR SATISFACTION
FROM THIS.
IT’S JUST TRUE.
BUT, TO BE HONEST, THAT’S WHAT
SCARES ME THE MOST.
MY BODY HAS NO CONTROL OVER
WHETHER OR NOT I LIVE OR DIE.
MY HEAD HAS THAT POWER.
AND IF SOMEONE WERE TO DESTROY
MY HEAD, THEN I WOULD DIE TOO,
NO MATTER WHAT I WANT OR WHERE
I AM!
I NEED YOU TO BELIEVE WHAT I’M
TELLING YOU.
I MAY NOT HAVE A BRAIN OR EYES,
BUT THIS GIVES ME NIGHTMARES.
I NEED YOU TO BELIEVE THAT THIS
THOUGHT TERRORIZES ME!
I’M SCARED OF THE FACT THAT MY
OWN DEATH MAY BE STARING ME IN
THE FACE, AND I WON’T EVEN SEE
IT COMING.
THAT’S WHY I WANT MY HEAD.
PLEASE TELL ME YOU BELIEVE THIS.
>> I TOLD YOU.
YOU’RE THE ONLY ONE I DO
BELIEVE.
THIS IS QUITE A CONUNDRUM.
BOTH OF US ARE GETTING VERY
UPSET BY SITUATIONS THAT ARE
SIMPLY HYPOTHETICAL.
>> YEAH, YOU’RE RIGHT.
HEY, SHINRA...
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> I NEED TO HIT YOU.
>> DO IT!
ALL RIGHT, NOW I GET TO HIT
YOU BACK.
>> UH.
>> PERFECT.
YOU’RE PRETTIEST WHEN YOU’RE
NOT HIDING YOUR FACE, YOU KNOW.
THAT PUNCH WAS A KISS...TO
CELEBRATE OUR MARRIAGE.
OKAY?
OW.
[groans]
ARE YOU CRYING?
>> THAT WAS QUITE ASTOUNDING.
MM?
>> [mutters]
>> YO, IZAYA.
>> DOTACHIN. BEEN AWHILE.
>> WILL YA STOP CALLIN’ ME THAT?
>> YEAH, ANYWAYS DO YOU KNOW
WHERE THE NAME THE DOLLARS COMES
FROM?
>> ISN’T IT SOMETHIN’ LIKE,
"GIMME ALL YOUR DOLLARS"?
>> NO, NOT EVEN CLOSE.
IT COMES FROM THE FACT THAT
THEY DON’T DO ANYTHING.
THEY JUST DAWDLE AROUND ALL DAY.
BUT "DOLLARS" SOUNDS COOLER.
>> DOTACHIN, TELL ME YOU SAW IT
TOO!
THE BLACK RIDER!
>> I TOTALLY CAN’T BELIEVE THAT
JUST HAPPENED.
I DIDN’T HALLUCINATE ALL THAT
CRAZINESS, DID I?
IT WAS LIKE A CG CHARACTER OR
SOMETHING.
>> THAT CG CHARACTER IS ALSO
PART OF THE DOLLARS.
>> both: WHAT? WOW!
>> IS THAT TRUE?
>> both: THAT IS SO COOL!
SO COOL. SO COOL.
>> I’M A LITTLE SHOCKED BY ALL
THIS.
I KNEW THERE WERE A LOT OF
PEOPLE ONLINE CLAIMING THAT
THEY WERE MEMBERS OF THE
DOLLARS.
HOWEVER, I HAD NO IDEA SO MANY
OF THEM WOULD ACTUALLY MAKE AN
EFFORT TO TURN UP WHEN A
MEETING WAS FINALLY CALLED.
[laughs]
HUMAN BEINGS DEFY IMAGINATION.
REMEMBER, I KNOW YOU CAME HERE
TO TOKYO HOPING TO ESCAPE THE
HUMDRUM, BUT IN ABOUT SIX
MONTHS, THIS’LL ALL SEEM
PRETTY ORDINARY TO YOU.
AT THAT RATE, YOU’LL HAVE TO
MOVE TO ANOTHER COUNTRY TO KEEP
THINGS EXCITING OR START
LOOKING FOR THINGS THAT ARE A
LITTLE MORE UNDERGROUND.
BUT I’D BE WILLING TO BET THAT
YOU WOULD GET BORED OF THAT IN
JUST A FEW DAYS AS WELL.
>> [breathes angrily]
>> THE ONLY WAY TO TRULY ESCAPE
THE MUNDANE IS FOR YOU TO
CONSTANTLY BE EVOLVING.
WHETHER YOU CHOOSE TO AIM HIGH
OR AIM LOW...
ENJOY EACH DAY FOR WHAT IT IS.
NOW, AS A SIGN OF RESPECT, I’VE
DECIDED NOT TO CHARGE YOU FOR
NAMIE YAGIRI’S PRIVATE CELL
PHONE NUMBER, AND I’M NOT
GONNA SELL YOU OUT ON BEING
THE FOUNDER OF THE DOLLARS.
IT’S YOUR ORGANIZATION.
USE IT HOWEVER YOU CHOOSE.
>> [whimpers]
>> [growls] IZAYA!
>> LOOKS LIKE IT’S TIME FOR ME
TO GO.
BEST OF LUCK TO YA,
TARO TANAKA!
>> GET BACK HERE, YOU BASTARD!
IZAYA!
>> WAS THAT...?
[cries out]
>> GET ’EM WHILE THEY’RE GOOD!
>> AND THAT WAS IT.
THE NEXT DAY, EVERYTHING WENT
BACK TO NORMAL.
FOR THIS GUY...
AND THAT GUY...
AND FOR THE BOY.
>> HEY, MIKADO.
GUESS WHAT I READ ONLINE.
THE DOLLARS HAD A HUGE MEETING
YESTERDAY!
THEY’RE SAYING IT WAS OFF THE
HOOK AND THAT SHIZUO AND SIMON
ARE TOTALLY PART OF ’EM!
AND THAT BLACK RIDER WAS THERE,
AND IT IS HEADLESS.
IT, LIKE, RODE DOWN WALLS.
AND IT HAS THIS SCYTHE, WHICH
IT WAS TOTALLY SWINGING AROUND
ALL CRAZY LIKE!
>> YOU’RE NOT MAKING ANY SENSE,
YOU KNOW.
>> AND EVEN FOR THOSE TWO.
>> I DON’T HAVE ANY LOVE FOR
YOU AT ALL.
BUT WHENEVER I SEE YOUR FACE,
I’M REMINDED OF THE PASSION
AND LOVE I HAVE FOR HER.
SO WITH THAT IN MIND, I’LL
ACCEPT YOUR LOVE...
UNTIL THE DAY I FINALLY GET HER
BACK.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> HEY, I’VE JUST BEEN HANGIN’
AROUND.
>> OH, HEY.
AFRAID I WON’T BE HERE LONG,
I’M KINDA TIRED TONIGHT.
>> WHAT, YOU PULL AN
ALL-NIGHTER?
>> YEAH, KINDA.
>> LOOKS LIKE KANRA STILL ISN’T
HERE YET.
>> WONDER IF KANRA WILL SHOW UP.
>> HEY, SOMETHING JUST CAME UP.
I GOTTA RUN.
>> YEAH, SURE.
>> SORRY. SEE YA LATER.
>> SEE YA.
>> HEY, SORRY, BUT A JOB JUST
CAME IN.
THEY SAID IT’S KINDA URGENT.
>> THAT’S FINE.
MY LIFE, IT WENT BACK TO
NORMAL AS WELL.
RUNNING ACROSS PEOPLE I’D
RATHER NOT MEET, JUST LIKE IT
WAS ANY OTHER DAY.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE YOU’VE MOVED
ON.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE ARE AFRAID OF
SPOOKY THINGS ’CAUSE THEY TEND
TO LURK IN THE DARK AND THEN
JUMP OUT AT YOU.
AFTER THAT LITTLE ENTRANCE YOU
MADE, I DOUBT ANYONE’S GONNA
BE SCARED OF YOU ANYMORE.
THINKING BACK, YOU DIDN’T KILL
ANYONE, DID YOU?
THAT SCYTHE ALL BARK AND NO
BITE.
I’M GUESSING YOU’RE GONNA GO
AFTER THAT WOMAN NOW.
I WOULD BE GLAD TO HELP YOU OUT
WITH THAT.
JUST CALL ME.
BYE NOW.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE
NAMIE YAGIRI WENT.
BUT I DON’T CARE. I’M ME...
AND THAT’S ENOUGH.
MY DAYS WERE ALWAYS PRETTY
UNCOMPLICATED, NOT TOO FULL OF
HOPE OR DESPAIR.
AND THEY’RE STILL LIKE THAT.
IT’S JUST THAT NOW I FIND THEM
INCREDIBLY SATISFYING.
HERE I AM, AND THERE YOU ARE.
IF YOU CAN FIND REDEMPTION IN
ME, THEN I CAN DO THE SAME
WITH YOU.
AND THE YOUNG BOY IS STILL
PONDERING HIS CONVERSATION WITH
IZAYA ORIHARA.
CAN A PERSON TRULY HAVE A LIFE
THAT’S ALWAYS NEW, ALWAYS FULL
OF EXCITEMENT AND POSSIBILITY?
OR IS IT JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE THAT TOO BECOMES PART OF
THE EVERYDAY?
>> HEY, I’M SORRY FOR
EVERYTHING.
>> AND THANK YOU.
>> [mutters]
>> WAIT A SEC.
THAT’S MY SEAT!
>> WELL, THERE’S A SPOT OPEN
BEHIND THE CLASS REP.
>> HUH?
WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
YOU CAN’T JUST SHOW UP AND TAKE
SOMEBODY’S SEAT.
>> AS FOR HER, CHANCES ARE SHE
WON’T BE SPENDING MUCH TIME
WITH MIKA HARIMA ANYMORE.
AND IN THE END, ONLY SHE WILL
KNOW IF THAT’S THE RIGHT
DECISION.
BUT THEN, MAYBE SHE WON’T.
IT’S RARE FOR A PERSON TO TRULY
UNDERSTAND THEIR OWN HEART.
AS SOMEONE ONCE SAID, THE
BEST THING YOU CAN DO IS KEEP
EVOLVING.
HE WAS EMPOWERED BY HIS
PREVIOUS ACTIONS, SO HE THOUGHT
HE COULD DO ANYTHING NOW.
BUT, UNFORTUNATELY, WHAT THE
YOUNG BOY HAD FAILED TO ACCOUNT
FOR WAS THE SHEER AMOUNT OF
COURAGE IT WOULD TAKE IN ORDER
FOR HIM TO ASK OUT HIS
CLASSMATE.
[breathes deeply]
IN 30 SECONDS, THE BOY WILL
FIND THE GIRL.
IN 35 SECONDS, THE BOY WILL
DISCOVER HIS BEST FRIEND
HITTING ON THE GIRL.
IN 45 SECONDS, THE BOY WILL
KICK THE CRAP OUT OF HIM.
IN 74 SECONDS, THE GIRL WILL
REJECT THE BOY’S OFFER TO GET
COFFEE.
AND, IN 78 SECONDS, THAT GIRL
WILL ASK THE BOY TO HAVE LUNCH
WITH HER ON THE ROOF.
HOW LONG WILL IT TAKE FOR HIM
TO FALL IN LOVE WITH HER?
AND HOW LONG BEFORE HE WORKS UP
THE NERVE TO TELL HER?
>> [laughs]
>> I GOTTA SAY...
THAT WAS VERY FOOLISH OF YOU.
YOU THREW AWAY EVERYTHING FOR
YOUR BROTHER’S TWISTED
VERSION OF LOVE.
[splash]
OR MAYBE IT WAS YOUR TWISTED
LOVE FOR YOUR BROTHER.
SO THIS CAN’T LOOK GOOD, CAN IT?
YOU’RE ABOUT TO MERGE WITH THE
NEBRA PEOPLE.
LET THEM CATCH WIND OF
SOMETHING LIKE THIS, AND, THE
NEXT THING YOU KNOW, YOU’VE GOT
SOME MAFIA HIT-MAN ON YOUR TAIL.
THEN AFTER THAT, POW!
AND CHECKMATE.
CLEANING CREW?
>> THAT’S THEM.
THAT’S THE NORMAL CREW THEY USE.
>> GOT IT.
[ringing]
HELLO.
THINGS ARE GETTING A LITTLE
BIT HEATED IN YOUR NECK OF THE
WOODS.
YOU SHOULD GET OUT OF THERE
SOON.
I WISH THE KING PIECES COULD
FIGHT EACH OTHER.
THEY SHOULD CHANGE THAT RULE.
I’VE GOTTA THINK THAT YOUR
UNCLE WAS A LOT LIKE ME.
HE QUESTIONED THE AFTERLIFE
MORE THAN ANYONE...
FEARED DEATH MORE THAN ANYONE...
AND LONGED FOR HEAVEN MORE THAN
ANYONE.
BUT THE AFTERLIFE, WELL, THAT I
BELIEVE IN
WE’LL JUST LEAVE IT AT THAT.
FOR WHATEVER REASON, DULLAHANS
ARE ALWAYS DEPICTED AS WOMEN IN
THE LEGENDS.
DO YOU KNOW WHY THAT IS?
>> NO, I DON’T.
MY MEN DID A LITTLE RESEARCH ON
THE MYTH, BUT, IN THE END, I
THOUGHT IT WAS A WASTE OF TIME.
>> YOU’RE ALWAYS THE PRAGMATIC
ONE.
WELL, SUIT YOURSELF.
THERE’S A PLACE CALLED VALHALLA.
IT’S SORT LIKE A HEAVEN.
AND, ACCORDING TO NORDIC
MYTHOLOGY, THE SOUL OF A FALLEN
WARRIOR IS GUIDED TO VALHALLA
BY AN ARMORED, FEMALE ANGEL
KNOWN AS A VALKYRIE.
A WOMAN WHO COMES TO GREET THE
DEAD.
DOESN’T THAT SOUND FAMILIAR?
SOME THEORIZE THAT A DULLAHAN
IS ACTUALLY A VALKYRIE WHO IS
WANDERING AROUND ON EARTH.
AND, IF THAT’S TRUE, THEN THIS
HEAD IS PROBABLY WAITING...
WAITING TO WAKE UP FOR WAR.
THEN SHE CAN FIND HER WARRIOR
AND TAKE HIM TO VALHALLA.
THAT’S WHY SHE’S ALIVE, BUT WITH
HER EYES CLOSED, BECAUSE WE
AREN’T ON A BATTLEFIELD.
IT’S MY WISH THAT SHE WOULD
CHOOSE ME AS HER WARRIOR.
IF THERE TRULY IS A VALHALLA
AWAITING ME AFTER DEATH, HOW
DO I EVEN PREPARE FOR THIS?
I MEAN, I KNOW I’M NOT REALLY
CUT OUT FOR BATTLEFIELD HEROICS.
SO THEN I’LL HAVE TO START A
WAR THAT ONLY I CAN WIN, RIGHT?
[laughs]
AREN’T I THE LUCKY ONE?
IMAGINE ME, WHO DOESN’T BELIEVE
IN A HEAVEN, MUCH LESS A
VIRTUOUS LIFE.
AND YET I STILL MEET AN ANGEL
OF DEATH WHO’S FALLEN TO EARTH.
>> WHATEVER.
THAT’S SIMPLY A THEORY OF YOURS.
>> WHOSOEVER BELIEVETH WILL BE
SAVED.
THIS IS JUST INSURANCE REALLY.
EVEN IF I DO END UP IN A HELL
SURROUNDED BY PAIN, AS LONG AS
I COULD EXIST, I WOULDN’T CARE.
BUT, THAT SAID, IF IT IS AT ALL
POSSIBLE, I WOULD STILL PREFER
HEAVEN.
HEY, NAMIE.
WHY DON’T WE ALL GO TO HEAVEN?
AS A MEMBER OF THE DOLLARS, I’M
GONNA KEEP THIS HIDING IN PLAIN
SIGHT.
THE LAST PLACE CELTY IS GOING
TO LOOK FOR HER HEAD IS WITHIN
THE SAME GANG THAT SHE BELONGS
TO.
I KNOW!
YOU SHOULD BECOME PART OF THE
DOLLARS TOO.
IT’S A LITTLE KNOWN FACT THAT
OUR BOSS DOESN’T TURN DOWN
ANYONE.
OF COURSE, AFTER A WHILE, I WAS
THE ONE WHO WAS INSTRUMENTAL IN
GATHERING PEOPLE.
I SAY WE GIVE THIS FALLEN ANGEL
A PAIR OF WINGS AGAIN.
WHAT DO YA THINK?
>> [singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
>> IN HER DAILY LIFE, NOTHING
EVER HAPPENS, NOTHING EVER
CHANGES, EVEN THOUGH THINGS ARE
BORN AND DISAPPEAR IN THE CITY
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
NEXT TIME, TAKES A SUDDEN TURN.