[Uragiri no Yuyake
by Theater Brook]
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> I’M MIKADO RYUGAMINE.
WOW, MASAOMI, NO WAY!
>> THERE AREN’T TOO MANY COLOR
GANGS ANYMORE.
BUT THEY CLASHED WITH THE GANGS
IN SAITAMA, AND MOST OF ’EM GOT
BUSTED.
>> ANRI SONOHARA.
IT’S NICE TO MEET YOU.
MIKA!
I’M SO SORRY!
>> YOU WANTED TO BE A REAL
IKUBUKURIAN.
THEN ACCEPT YOUR CHALLENGE.
>> THERE YOU ARE.
I FOUND YOU, MY LOVE.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> [panting]
[gasps]
I’M SORRY.
REALLY, I AM.
I TELL YOU WHAT, I’LL GIVE IT
BACK.
JUST LET ME GO.
[gasps]
[whimpering]
AAH!
>> THIS IS BAD.
REALLY BAD.
>> OH, IT’S MY FAULT, CELTY.
IT WASN’T EVEN THAT GREAT OF A
JOB.
I DON’T KNOW WHY I TOOK IT.
>> THE JOB ITSELF SHOULD HAVE
BEEN PRETTY EASY.
BUT THE FROM OUT OF NOWHERE,
THAT THING SHOWED UP.
>> AAH!
[whimpering]
AAH!
>> [supernatural voice] INHUMAN
MONSTER, MONSTER, MONSTER!
>> YOU HEARD A VOICE COME FROM
YOUR WOUND?
>> IT SAID THAT I WAS A MONSTER.
>> WELL, NOW THAT’S JUST RUDE.
I PREFER ENCHANTRESS,
PERSONALLY.
>> WHAT WAS IT?
>> UH...
[typing on keypad]
>> WHAT IF IT WAS SOME KIND OF
ALIEN?
>> CELTY, WAS THAT SUPPOSED TO
BE A JOKE?
>> [panting] MO-MONSTER!
>> all: HUH?
>> [panting]
>> HEH, LET’S GO!
>> both: [panting]
>> SOMETIMES IT SEEMS THIS CITY
IS ONLY MADE UP OF PRANKS,
IMPULSES, AND CHANCE.
AND THIS COULD JUST BE ANOTHER
ONE OF GOD’S PRANKS OR IMPULSES.
HERE I AM, WALKING HOME NEXT TO
A CHICK THAT EASILY TOPS MY LIST
OF THE 37 GIRLS I FELL IN LOVE
WITH ON THE FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL.
SHE’S A FIRST-RATE HOTTIE WITH
GLASSES.
AND THEN THIS DORK SHOWS UP.
TOTALLY BLOWS.
>> YOU TOOK SOME GUFF THE OTHER
DAY.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> UH...
>> [thinking to himself]
THIS SO ISN’T WORKING.
[speaking aloud]
I SURE DIDN’T SEE THAT COMING,
YOU PUTTING THE MOVES ON HER
BEFORE ME.
>> THAT ISN’T WHAT I WAS DOING.
>> AAH!
>> HUH? WHAT THE--MIKADO!
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT’S ALL GOOD.
I THINK IF I WERE YOU, THOUGH,
I WOULD HAVE TAKEN THAT SHOT AND
SCORED.
BY NOW I’D BE WHISPERING SWEET
NOTHINGS TO HER IN WESTGATE
PARK.
DUMP THE CHUMP AND GO OUT WITH
ME!
[both gasping]
>> HEY, WHAT ARE YOU--
>> UM, I’M NOT--
>> IT’S ALL RIGHT, YOU DON’T
NEED TO ANSWER RIGHT AWAY.
I’VE GOT THE SAME OFFER OUT TO
SEVEN OTHER GIRLS AND I STILL
DON’T KNOW WHICH ONE I WANT
MOST.
>> DON’T WASTE YOUR TIME TRYING
TO MAKE SENSE OF THIS GUY, ANRI,
IT’LL JUST MAKE YOUR HEAD HURT.
I KNOW HE LIKES TO ACT LIKE A
PLAYBOY, BUT HE’S FAR FROM IT.
LAST TIME HE HIT ON A GIRL--
>> OKAY, YOU’VE SAID ENOUGH!
>> EH?
>> HI-YAA!
>> OH!
>> THIS GUY IS MIKADO RYUGAMINE,
MY BEST FRIEND.
HE COMES FROM THE STICKS AND HAS
JUST BEEN IN IKEBUKURO A FEW
DAYS.
HE’S PRETTY NAIVE BUT ALSO
REALLY STUBBORN, SO I CAN
NEVER LEAVE HIM ALONE.
AND IT SEEMS THIS NOOB AND I
HAVE ENDED UP IN A BIT OF A LOVE
TRIANGLE.
I GUESS THAT’S PART OF BEING
YOUNG.
EEE!
>> OW!
OOH, THAT’S SO MEAN.
>> I CAN TELL YOU’RE GOOD
FRIENDS.
>> YEAH, BEST FRIENDS.
>> IT’S THE CROSS I BEAR.
>> HEE-HEE!
>> YEAH, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY!
>> AS FOR HOW WE ENDED UP IN
THIS MESS...
WELL, THAT GOES BACK TO THE
FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL.
>> SEIJI YAGIRI, IT’S NICE TO
MEET ALL OF YOU.
>> THANK YOU, SEIJI, THAT’LL BE
ENOUGH.
PLEASE TAKE YOUR SEAT AND WE’LL
MOVE ON.
>> NO, SIR.
>> all: HUH?
>> LISTEN, I JUST WANNA SAY I
WON’T BE AT SCHOOL FOR A WHILE.
WELL, ACTUALLY I’LL NEVER BE
BACK.
I HAVE MY REASONS.
THIS IS SOMETHING VERY
IMPORTANT TO ME.
I GOTTA GO, I CAN’T WASTE ANY
MORE TIME WITH YOU PEOPLE.
GOOD-BYE, SIR.
>> UH, SEIJI, WAIT, PLEASE.
JUST HOLD ON A SECOND.
>> WHEN MIKADO TOLD ME THAT
STORY, MY FIRST THOUGHT WAS--
>> SEIJI, WAIT!
>> WOW, IT TAKES ALL KINDS TO
MAKE THIS WORLD.
>> PLEASE, WAIT.
>> AND THAT WAS THE MOMENT I
FELL IN LOVE.
CUTE LITTLE SMILE, BITCHIN’
BOOBS--I GUESS SHE WASN’T
SMILING, WHATEVER.
>> I SAID I DON’T KNOW ANYTHING!
>> WAIT, HOLD ON!
>> HELLO!
HEY, YOU GOOD DOWN THERE?
WELL, THAT’S THE SHORT OF HOW
SHE FOUND HERSELF AT THE VERY
TOP OF MY POTENTIAL GIRLFRIEND
LIST.
AND THEN...
>> HEY, ANRI.
YOU HEADING HOME NOW?
>> YEAH.
>> EVERYTHING OKAY, ANRI?
IF SOMETHING IS BOTHERING YOU,
YOU CAN TELL ME.
I’M CONCERNED.
IF THERE’S A BULLY OR YOU’RE IN
TROUBLE, LET ME KNOW.
>> I’M FINE.
>> YOU’RE SURE THERE ISN’T
SOMETHING YOU WANNA TALK ABOUT?
>> NO, I’M FINE.
>> OKAY, YOU KNOW, I HAVEN’T
SEEN HARIMA COME TO SCHOOL YET.
EVEN THOUGH YOU’RE BOTH IN THE
SAME CLASS NOW.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW IT WASN’T
EASY MAKING THAT HAPPEN.
I TALKED TO MR. SAITOU FROM YOUR
JUNIOR HIGH.
HE TOLD ME TO MAKE SURE THAT
I TAKE EXTRA SPECIAL CARE
OF YOU, SO YOU CAN TELL ME
ANYTHING YOU WANT, OKAY?
I KNOW--WHY DON’T I TAKE YOU
HOME TODAY?
DID YOU HEAR?
THE SLASHER WAS IN IKEBUKURO
AGAIN.
>> MM.
>> MR. NASUJIMA, ARE YOU
SEXUALLY HARASSING HER?
>> UH...
>> UNH!
>> WOW, YOU SURE WERE GETTING
PRETTY HANDSY THERE WITH OUR
CLASS REP, TEACH.
I MEAN, IF THAT WASN’T SEXUAL
HARASSMENT, THEN I SURE DON’T
KNOW WHAT IS.
SO YOU LIKE THE SEXY HOROSHO
TYPES.
>> KIDA, ENOUGH WITH THE
CLOWNING.
ANRI, I WOULDN’T WANT YOU TO GET
THE WRONG IDEA AND START
SPREADING RUMORS.
>> DOES SHE REALLY SEEM LIKE THE
GOSSIPY TYPE TO YOU?
>> NO, YOU’VE GOT A POINT.
YOU KIDS TAKE CARE.
[chuckles]
>> AND YOU HAVE NOTHING TO WORRY
ABOUT.
THE ONLY ONE SPREADING RUMORS
WILL BE ME.
>> OH! AAH!
>> [chuckles] TOTALLY HEROIC,
RIGHT?
CAN YOU GET MORE AWESOME THAN
ME?
HOW CAN SHE NOT BE IN LOVE RIGHT
NOW?
>> MASAOMI, ANRI.
>> OF COURSE THIS IS WHEN YOU
WOULD SHOW UP.
HERE YOU GO, ALL YOURS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HEY, SERIOUSLY, WATCH OUT FOR
THAT GUY.
HE’S BAD NEWS.
MOST OF IT IS JUST RUMORS, BUT
NASUJIMA REALLY DID GO AFTER A
STUDENT ONCE.
>> HE DID WHAT?
>> YEAH, AN OLDER STUDENT NAMED
HARUNA NIEKAWA.
SHE TRANSFERRED OUT SECOND
SEMESTER OF LAST YEAR.
WORD ABOUT THEM DATING SPREAD
QUICKLY, THEN THEY BROKE THINGS
OFF SO HE WOULDN’T GET BUSTED.
>> REALLY?
>> MAYBE NASUJIMA OR THE SCHOOL
MADE HER LEAVE, OR SHE LEFT ON
HER OWN.
EITHER WAY, SHE’S NOT HERE THIS
YEAR.
HEY, IF HE MESSES WITH YOU,
MIKADO AND I WILL TAKE HIM OUT.
WON’T WE, BUDDY?
>> UH, YEAH.
I’M NOT REALLY SURE WHAT I’M
SUPPOSED TO DO, BUT IF YOU NEED
MY HELP, I’M GLAD TO DO IT.
>> DUDE, WRONG LINE.
YOU’RE SUPPOSED TO BE ALL,
"I DON’T KNOW WHAT I’M DOING,
BUT LOVE IS THE WIND BENEATH MY
WINGS."
[eats ice cream]
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
OTHERWISE YOU’RE A PUSS.
>> HEY, HAVE SOME MANNERS.
>> IT’S JUST THE TRUTH.
>> ANYWAY, ABOUT THOSE GIRLS.
>> HMM?
>> THE ONES THAT WERE BULLYING
YOU.
THEY’RE FROM YOUR JUNIOR HIGH,
RIGHT?
>> HOW--HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
>> WELL, IT WAS JUST SOME OF THE
THINGS THEY SAID TO YOU.
IT SEEMED LIKE THERE MIGHT HAVE
BEEN SOME OTHER GIRL AROUND WHO
USED TO STICK UP FOR YOU.
BUT I GUESS THAT GIRL’S GONE NOW
AND SO THOSE GIRLS CAME BACK TO
HARASS YOU AGAIN.
>> YEAH, THAT’S RIGHT.
A FRIEND OF YOURS WHO’S
DISAPPEARED--STILL NO SIGN OF
HER YET?
>> IT’S MIKA HARIMA FROM OUR
CLASS, RIGHT?
>> THEY’RE SAYING THAT SHE’S
JUST ABSENT FROM SCHOOL RIGHT
NOW, BUT SHE’S BEEN MISSING
SINCE BEFORE SCHOOL EVEN
STARTED.
>> SHOULDN’T WE TELL THE COPS
ABOUT THIS?
THE LAST I HEARD FROM HER, SHE
HAD SENT A TEXT TO ME AND HER
FAMILY.
SHE SAID HER HEART WAS BROKEN
AND SO SHE WAS TAKING A QUICK
TRIP AND NOT TO WORRY.
>> HER HEART WAS BROKEN?
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WELL, SHE--LISTEN, THIS MIGHT
COME AS A BIT OF A SHOCK TO
YOU--
>> AFTER ALL I’VE SEEN THESE
PAST FEW DAYS, I DOUBT ANYTHING
CAN SHOCK ME.
>> MY FRIEND MIKA...
IS A STALKER.
>> [coughs]
BLAGH!
>> GOTCHA, SO THAT GUY WE
OVERHEARD YOU TALKING TO
EARLIER--MIKA WAS STALKING HIM.
NO, SORRY, SHE WAS DEEPLY IN
LOVE WITH HIM AND HAD TO GO ON A
TRIP BECAUSE HE REJECTED HER.
>> MM-HMM.
>> THAT’S AN ISSUE FOR HER
FAMILY, THEN, NOT YOU.
IF SHE DOESN’T COME BACK SOON,
THEY’LL CALL THE COPS.
>> MM.
>> WERE THE TWO OF YOU CLOSE?
WERE YOU GOOD FRIENDS?
>> WHY IS HE ASKING HER THAT?
>> WELL, WE WERE TOGETHER ALL
THE TIME.
>> WHOA, HIS INTUITION IS ODDLY
GOOD.
>> I’M NOT NATURALLY VERY
SOCIAL, BUT SHE DRAGGED ME ALONG
WHEREVER SHE WENT.
AND IT WAS ONLY BECAUSE OF HER
I ACTUALLY MET PEOPLE.
THEN WHEN I FOUND OUT SHE CHOSE
THE SAME HIGH SCHOOL I DID,
I ACTUALLY FELT KINDA GUILTY
ABOUT IT.
>> SO THEN--
>> MIKADO, I KNOW WHAT YOU’RE
THINKING--THAT MIKA ONLY KEPT
ANRI AROUND TO MAKE HERSELF LOOK
BETTER.
BUT DUDE, DON’T SAY THAT.
>> I KNOW.
>> both: HUH?
>> KNOW WHAT?
>> THAT MIKA WAS ONLY USING ME
TO MAKE HERSELF LOOK BETTER.
BUT TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST,
I WAS USING HER TOO.
DEPENDING ON HER MADE MY LIFE
EASIER.
PRETTY SOON I COULDN’T IMAGINE
LIVING ANY OTHER WAY.
>> UM...
>> BUT NOW I THINK I’M OKAY.
I’VE REALIZED THAT I DON’T
REALLY NEED HER.
I’M USED TO IT NOW.
I’M DOING FINE WITHOUT HER.
TO TELL YOU GUYS THE TRUTH,
I ONLY ASKED TO BE CLASS REP
BECAUSE THAT’S THE JOB SHE
WANTED.
I FIGURED I SHOULD JUST DO IT IN
HER PLACE.
I WANTED TO PROVE TO MYSELF THAT
I CAN BE BETTER THAN SHE IS.
YOU THINK I’M DEVIOUS, DON’T
YOU?
>> ACTUALLY I THINK IT’S DEVIOUS
THAT YOU’RE TELLING US THIS.
>> OH.
>> IT KINDA SEEMS LIKE YOU’RE
ASKING FOR OUR FORGIVENESS OR
SOMETHING.
THE FACT THAT YOU WANNA BE
BETTER THAN HER IS NOT SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD FEEL THE NEED TO
DEFEND.
IF YOU ASK ME, THAT’S SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD REALLY OWN AND BE
PROUD OF.
UH, BUT...
>> YOU’RE SO RIGHT.
THANK YOU, MIKADO.
>> I’VE GOTTA SAY, I DO DIG THIS
SIDE OF HIM.
[giggles] YAA!
>> AAH! OOF.
>> [chuckles]
>> MASAOMI.
>> [laughs] YOU’RE LAME!
>> WHY AM I LAME?
>> WHAT? THE TOUGHEST GUY IN
IKEBUKURO?
>> YEAH, WHO IS IT?
>> ARE YOU WITH SOME MAGAZINE?
TOUGHEST? HOW LAME ARE YOU?
>> YOU KNOW WHO I THINK IS THE
MOST SCARY?
THAT GUY ON THE BLACK BIKE.
>> I KNOW HIM.
HE’S, LIKE, GOT NO HEAD.
>> NO WAY.
>> BUT THEN AGAIN, THERE’S THAT
SLASHER.
>> OH, RIGHT, YEAH.
WOULDN’T YOU GUYS SAY THE
DOLLARS ARE PRETTY HARD CORE
RIGHT NOW?
>> THE DOLLARS?
>> all: YEAH, THE DOLLARS.
>> HUH?
>> THANKS FOR EVERYTHING TODAY.
I SHOULD REALLY BE GETTING HOME.
>> ALL RIGHT, SEE YA.
>> GOOD-BYE, MY DEAR ANRI.
[laughs]
>> YOU KNOW, I STARTED THINKING.
I’LL BET SEIJI AND HER FRIEND
MIKA MIGHT ACTUALLY BE TOGETHER
RIGHT NOW.
>> THE STALKER GOT THE STALKEE?
>> I DON’T KNOW, I’M NOT SURE.
MAYBE SHE KIDNAPPED HIM OR
SOMETHING.
>> MORE LIKELY.
>> IF WE WANTED TO, HOW COULD WE
FIND HER?
>> I SAY DROP IT.
ANRI SAID SHE’S FINE.
>> YOU WOULD NEED A MASSIVE
ORGANIZATION FOR SOMETHING LIKE
THIS, LIKE THE DOLLARS.
>> MIKADO, DON’T TELL ME YOU’RE
SERIOUSLY THINKING ABOUT JOINING
THE DOLLARS.
>> UH, NO. NO WAY.
>> YOU DON’T WANT THAT.
COLOR GANGS ARE THE KIND OF
THING THAT YOU DO WHEN YOU’RE
YOUNG, AND THEN JUST REGRET IT
WHEN YOU’RE OLDER.
>> YEAH, BUT YOU’VE GOTTA DO
CERTAIN THINGS WHEN YOU’RE
YOUNG.
>> DUDE, I’M TOTALLY SPENT
RIGHT NOW.
[can clangs]
I AIN’T DOING NOTHING.
>> I HAD SOME SERIOUS
DEPRESSION GOIN’ ON BEFORE
MIKADO CAME TO IKEBUKURO.
I AM WHO I AM NOW ONLY BECAUSE
A LOT OF PEOPLE HELPED ME OUT,
AND ONE OF THEM WAS DEFINITELY
MIKADO.
HE’S JUST KINDA DROPPED IN TO
IKEBUKURO, AND I CAN TELL THE
CITY’S TOO MUCH FOR HIM.
HE LOOKS SO VULNERABLE HERE,
AND IT WORRIES ME.
I COULD COOL HIM DOWN BY TAKING
HIM TO PLACES A LITTLE MORE
CHILL, BUT I SEE THAT LOOK IN
HIS EYES AND I KNOW HE DIGS IT
HERE.
SO INSTEAD I JUST TRY TO STICK
WITH HIM AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
IF I HAD MY WAY, HE’D NEVER HAVE
TO SEE THE DARKNESS THAT LURKS
IN THIS PLACE.
AND NEITHER WOULD I.
BANG.
[water rushing]
I PROMISED MYSELF THAT I WOULD
NEVER GO THERE AGAIN.
[police siren wailing]
>> AAH!
AAH!
>> WAS THAT A TROLL JUST NOW?
>> MORE LIKE AN ALIEN.
>> MAYBE THEY WERE LAUGHING.
>> SOUNDED PRETTY SCARY.
>> BUT THEN, WHAT’S WITH THE
"HA-HA?"
>> NO, I MEAN, ALIENS ARE SCARY.
NOT THE OTHER GUY.
>> TSUMI UTA?
YOU KNOW THAT KANJI COULD READ
"ZAIKA."
>> AS IN "WEALTH"?
>> I’LL TAKE A LOOK AT IT LATER.
IN THE MEANTIME, YOU’VE GOT A
JOB.
IT’S FROM MR. SHIKI WITH THE
AWAKUSU, SO IT’S NOT ENTIRELY
ON THE LEVEL.
DO YOU STILL WANT IT?
>> MORE TRANSPORTING?
>> YUP, EXACTLY.
BUT YOU’VE GOTTA GET THIS
OBJECT BACK BEFORE YOU DELIVER
IT.
NOW I DIDN’T ASK HIM WHAT IT
WAS.
I’M GUESSING IT’S BEST FOR
BOTH PARTIES IF I DON’T KNOW.
>> I GOTCHA.
>> GREAT, THEN ABOUT THE GOODS.
SEEMS THE GUY WHO HAS IT KEEPS
MOVING.
WE’VE GOT GOOD INFO ON WHERE HE
LIKES TO LAY LOW, SO FINDING HIM
SHOULDN’T BE AN ISSUE, OKAY?
>> GOT IT.
>> THERE HAVE BEEN A LOT MORE
SPOTTINGS OF THE SLASHER LATELY.
BE CAREFUL OUT THERE.
>> SLASHER?
>> UH-HUH, THAT’S WHAT I SAID.
THAT SLASHER IS UNHINGED.
>> THEY SAY IT COMES OUT OF
NOWHERE AND BEATS YOU TO A PULP.
>> DUDE, HOW TOUGH CAN IT BE IF
IT LETS YOU LIVE?
THE FIERCEST GUY AROUND HERE HAS
GOTTA BE SIMON FROM
RUSSIA SUSHI.
>> YEAH, OR MAYBE THAT INTEL
BROKER WHO MOVED TO SHINJUKU.
>> IZAYA ORIHARA.
>> OH, NO, IT’S GOTTA BE THAT
OTHER CAT--
>> all: SHIZUO HEIWAJIMA!
>> [panting]
>> WHAT’S THE MOST BADASS COLOR
GANG RIGHT NOW?
THE DOLLARS, DUDE.
>> THEY DON’T EVEN HAVE A COLOR.
UP UNTIL LAST YEAR THOUGH IT WAS
THOSE YELLOW BASTARDS.
>> YELLOW?
>> YEAH, THEY CALL THEMSELVES
THE YELLOW SCARVES.
>> THEY WENT FULL TILT WITH A
GANG CALLED THE BLUE SQUARES.
IT WAS SO GNARLY IT WIPED OUT
BOTH GANGS.
>> NAH, WORD IS NOW THE YELLOW
SCARVES ARE BACK.
>> COME ON.
YOU COME ORDER MORE,
YOU EAT MORE.
WE GOT ENGAWA AND SCALLOPS
TODAY.
>> DOESN’T IT SEEM LIKE WE’VE
BEEN SEEING HIM A LOT LATELY?
>> SEEING WHAT?
>> MM, THOSE YELLOW GUYS, RIGHT?
I’VE SEEN THEM TOO.
>> WAIT A MINUTE, YOU MEAN--
>> both: THE YELLOW DWARVES!
>> THE YELLOW SCARVES.
>> YEAH, THAT’S IT.
THAT ONE WAS A MESS.
>> NAH, THOSE GUYS GOT THEIR
ASSES HANDED TO THEM BY THE BLUE
SQUARES AND THEN DISSOLVED.
>> THAT’S RIGHT, THEN THEIR BOSS
BACKED OFF FROM THE GANG THING
AND RETIRED OR SOMETHING.
>> WELCOME, FRIEND.
>> I WAS HOPING YOU COULD TELL
ME ABOUT THE DOLLARS.
>> WHAT?
>> I’M TRYING TO KEEP A FRIEND
OF MINE FROM GETTING MIXED UP
WITH THEM.
>> WHY ARE YOU ASKING US?
>> WELL, YOU’RE THE ONLY ONE I
CAN TALK TO.
>> GUESS YOU CAN’T REALLY ASK
IZAYA ORIHARA ABOUT IT, HUH?
>> LOOK, THEY’RE KIND OF A
MYSTERY.
WE DON’T KNOW A WHOLE LOT ABOUT
THEM EITHER.
BUT SINCE YOU’RE HERE, I’LL TELL
YOU WHAT WE DO KNOW.
>> SOMETIMES I FEEL LIKE THIS
TOWN WILL SWALLOW ME WHOLE.
BUT I’LL NEVER LET THAT DARKNESS
FIND MIKADO.
>> OH.
>> MIKADO?
SORRY.
>> OH, IT’S GONNA TAKE MORE THAN
THAT.
>> IN CASE YOU HADN’T NOTICED,
DORK, YOU JUST BUMPED INTO THE
YELLOW SCARVES.
>> SEIJI!
WHO’S SHE?
THAT’S NOT MIKA HARIMA.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHO YOU ARE,
AND WE’RE ON A ROMANTIC GETAWAY,
SO LEAVE.
>> A ROMANTIC GETAWAY?
>> LET’S GO.
>> IF THAT’S NOT MIKA, WHO IS
IT?
OH.
MASAOMI?
>> [gasps]
[whimpering]
>> INTERESTING, YOU SAY YOU’RE
WITH THE YELLOW SCARVES.
>> YOU DON’T JOKE ABOUT THAT.
>> I SAID IT BECAUSE I DOUBT IT.
>> AAH! YOU LITTLE--
>> MA-MASAOMI!
>> HUH?
>> OH!
MIKADO, WHY YOU GOTTA SHOW UP
NOW?
>> OH!
[panting]
MO-MONSTER!
>> all: HUH?
>> [whimpering]
>> LET’S GO.
>> HUH?
[whimpering]
[blood splattering]
>> AAH!
[both panting]
[both laughing]
>> MAN, YOU HAD ME SO WORRIED.
>> YOU HAD ME WORRIED TOO.
>> I GUESS, TRUTH BE TOLD,
I’M THE ONE WHO’S BECOME
DEPENDENT UPON HIM.
SINCE MIKADO CAME HERE, MY FALSE
SENSE OF BRAVADO IS TURNING INTO
SOMETHING REAL.
MAYBE NEXT TIME I’LL BE ABLE TO
SEE HER WITHOUT TURNING AND
RUNNING AWAY.
[knock on door]
>> YES?
>> I WASN’T SURE I COULD EVER
FEEL LIKE THIS.
>> WOW, I DIDN’T THINK YOU’D
COME HERE AGAIN.
HI, IZAYA.
>> HELLO.
SO HOW IS HE?
>> WELL, HE DOES COME BY HERE
SOMETIMES, BUT THAT’S AS FAR AS
HE GOES.
MM.
>> I’M BACK.
HARUNA, HAVE YOU EATEN YET?
HARUNA?
[typing on keyboard]
>> SO I BANNED THAT TROLL WHO
WAS BOTHERING US.
>> THINGS SHOULD GO BACK TO
NORMAL.
>> LET’S HOPE SO.
>> HAVE YOU HEARD THE LATEST
ABOUT THE YELLOW SCARVES?
THEY GOT HIT BY THE SLASHER
YESTERDAY.
>> WHAT ARE THE YELLOW SCARVES?
>> I WONDER IF THE SLASHER IS
PART OF THE DOLLARS.
>> THEY CAN’T BE.
>> THERE MIGHT BE A WAR BREWING.
>> IT MAY NOT LOOK LIKE IT AT
FIRST, BUT EVERYTHING THAT
HAPPENS IN THIS TOWN IS SOMEHOW
RELATED.
YO!
IT’S ALL PART OF SOME LARGER,
AWFUL TRUTH THAT’S BEYOND OUR
COMPREHENSION.
HOWEVER...
HMM.
>> WHA--
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> HEY, ANRI, GOOD MORNING.
>> I MAY BE SLOW TO REALIZE
THIS, BUT I’M OKAY WITH THIS
LITTLE TRIANGLE WE GOT GOIN’ ON.
YOU KNOW, EVEN IF THINGS TAKE A
TURN FOR THE WORSE AND THE DOTS
CONNECT IN WAYS I CAN’T FORESEE,
I BELIEVE THIS RELATIONSHIP
WON’T CHANGE.
THAT IT CAN WEATHER WHATEVER
STORM LIES AHEAD.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> THE DOLLARS, I CAN’T SAY MUCH
ABOUT THEM.
HOWEVER, I CAN TELL YOU ABOUT
WHAT IS NOW THE LEGENDARY
KAZUTANO INCIDENT.
NEXT TIME, ACTIVE INTEREST.
THAT IS, AS LONG AS YOU DON’T
CALL ME DOTACHIN.