[Uragiri no Yuyake
by Theater Brook]
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> WHAT ARE YOU ASKING ABOUT THE
DOLLARS FOR, ANYWAY?
>> DON’T TELL ME YOU’RE
SERIOUSLY THINKING ABOUT JOINING
THE DOLLARS.
>> WHAT THE HELL KIND OF ANSWER
IS THAT?!
>> WHY IS SOME OTHER BODY
WALKING AROUND WITH MY HEAD ON
ITS SHOULDERS?
>> MAYBE YOUR HEAD STUMBLED
ACROSS A FRESH CORPSE.
>> THIS’LL BE FUN.
THIS’LL BE FUN.
>> IF THE POLICE COME ACROSS
THAT THING BEFORE WE DO,
THAT WON’T WORK OUT WELL FOR US.
I WANT HER DEAD OR ALIVE.
IF YOU HAVE ANY TROUBLE BRINGING
HER BACK, THEN DISPOSE OF HER.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> [sighs]
I DON’T KNOW.
THINGS ARE KIND OF TIGHT THIS
MONTH.
ALL RIGHT, I ALSO HAVE TO GET A
SPONGE FOR THE KITCHEN.
>> THANK YOU, HAVE A NICE DAY!
>> [sighs]
[horse neighing]
THE BLACK BIKE!
IT SHOULD BE RIGHT AROUND THAT
CORNER...
[exclamations]
I’M SO SORRY!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU’RE THAT...
>> SAVE ME!
>> HUH? HUH?
>> [gasps]
>> SAVE ME!
>> HEY!
[girls shrieking]
>> THE RIDER.
>> THE BLACK RIDER!
>> OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS SO COOL!
>> I CAN’T BELIEVE IT.
I JUST TOTALLY GOT ITS PICTURE!
>> I’M SO POSTING THIS.
[giggling]
>> HUH.
SO YOU JUST BUMPED INTO THIS
BEAUTIFUL GIRL ON THE STREET
WHO LOST HER MEMORIES AND IS
BEING CHASED BY THE BLACK RIDER.
AND BY THE TIME I GET HERE,
THIS CHICK HAS ALREADY GONE TO
SLEEP.
AND YOU REALLY THINK I’M GONNA
BELIEVE THIS WILD-ASS STORY
YOU’VE CONCOCTED?
>> I’M TELLING YOU, MAN, IT’S
REALLY THE TRUTH.
>> IF THIS TOOK PLACE IN THE
MORNING AND IT MADE YOU LATE
FOR SCHOOL, IT’D BE WAY BETTER.
OH, AND IF SHE WERE A TRANSFER
STUDENT TOO, GENIUS!
NO, NO, WAIT.
SHE’S A PRINCESS AND YOUR
LONG-LOST FRIEND.
NOW THAT’S PERFECT!
TELL ME, ARE YOU CATCHING MY
WITTY SARCASM HERE OR NOT?
>> YEAH, BUT IF YOU HAVE TO
EXPLAIN IT, THEN IT’S NOT SO
WITTY.
[sighs]
SHE SAYS SHE CAN’T REMEMBER
ANYTHING AND SHE WON’T LET ME GO
TO THE POLICE.
I DON’T KNOW WHAT ELSE I SHOULD
DO.
>> HMM, YOU’LL JUST HAVE TO KEEP
AN EYE ON HER.
LET HER SLEEP FOR NOW.
AND THEN TOMORROW, WHEN SHE
WAKES UP, SEE IF SHE FEELS ANY
DIFFERENT.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, SEE YA TOMORROW.
>> COOL.
THANKS FOR COMING SO LATE.
THE BLACK RIDER KNOWS MY FACE
NOW.
IF THAT URBAN LEGEND IS ACTUALLY
TRUE...
WHAT IF THAT THING COMES AFTER
ME?
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
I USED TO HATE MY ORDINARY
LIFE.
>> all: GOOD MORNING.
>> I WANTED MY LIFE TO BE
DIFFERENT THAN EVERYONE ELSE’S.
I GUESS THAT’S ONE OF THE
REASONS WHY I’M LETTING HER
STAY HERE.
THERE’S ONE THING I DIDN’T
TELL MASAOMI ABOUT--HER SCAR.
IT’S ALMOST AS IF SOMEONE
SAWED OFF HER HEAD...
AND THEN SEWED IT BACK ON AGAIN.
>> WE HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT FROM
THE STUDENT STORE.
THEY ARE CURRENTLY SOLD OUT OF
THE JUMBO MELON BREAD...
>> YO, MIKADO!
HOW’S THAT SLEEPING BEAUTY YOU
GOT STASHED AT YOUR PLACE?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SHH! SHH!
>> WHAT? YOU GOT SOME CHICK
STAYING WITH YOU?
>> I’D TRY TO KEEP THAT ON
THE DOWN-LOW TOO.
>> CHECK IT OUT.
HE WAS JUST ROUNDING A CORNER
AND BUMPS INTO A CUTIE WITH
AMNESIA WHO’S BEING CHASED BY
BAD GUYS.
AND WHO’S SHE LIVING WITH NOW?
THIS GUY.
>> YEAH, NO WAY.
KIRIGAMINE’S JUST MAKING THAT
SHIT UP.
>> NO, IT’S RYUGAMINE.
>> HEY, DOES SOMEONE WANNA BUY
MY LUNCH TICKETS?
>> REALLY?
>> [laughs nervously]
>> SEE?
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT BECAUSE
NO ONE BELIEVES IT.
SO HOW’S THE HOTTIE?
>> I DON’T KNOW.
SHE WAS STILL ASLEEP WHEN I
LEFT.
>> SLEEPING BEAUTY’S PRETTY
SLEEPY.
ALL RIGHT.
LET’S GET TO THE POINT.
>> WHAT POINT?
>> YEAH, THE POINT AS TO WHY I’M
MACKIN’ DOWN IN FOURTH PERIOD.
IT’S SO THAT I CAN FREE MYSELF
UP ON THE LUNCH BREAK.
>> THE DOLLARS POLL?
>> DUDE, THIS IS LIKE THE HOT
TOPIC RIGHT NOW IN OUR CLASS.
THESE DOLLARS ARE TOTALLY
SHROUDED IN MYSTERY.
SO IF YOU SAW SOMEONE AND
THOUGHT, "THAT DUDE SO LOOKS
LIKE HE’S IN THE DOLLARS,"
THEN FIND HIS NAME ON THE LIST
AND VOTE FOR HIM!
>> WOW, SOME PEOPLE ARE
GETTIN’ A LOT OF VOTES.
>> YOU CAN VOTE FOR AS MANY
PEOPLE AS YOU WANT.
>> HEY!
THAT TAKIGUCHI GUY FROM 1D HAS
JUST RECEIVED ONE VOTE SO FAR.
>> THANK YOU FOR NOTICING.
THAT’S RIGHT.
ONE VOTE...
FROM NONE OTHER THAN YOURS
TRULY.
SEE, ME AND THAT GUY HAVE GYM
CLASS TOGETHER, AND I WAS LIKE,
"YEAH, THAT DUDE’S GOTTA BE IN
THE DOLLARS, MM-HMM."
>> WHAT MAKES YOU THINK THAT?
>> HUNCH.
>> [laughs]
>> AND NOW I’M OFF TO FIND OUT
FOR SURE.
>> W-WAIT A SEC.
>> EXCUSE ME!
IS RYOU TAKIGUCHI AROUND NOW?
>> HUH?
>> HE’S NOT HERE.
>> DID HE GO TO EAT?
>> BET HE’S UP ON THE ROOF.
THAT’S WHERE HE USUALLY HANGS
OUT ON LUNCH BREAK.
>> I BET HE WENT UP THERE TO
SMOKE A STOGIE.
>> ARE YOU REALLY SURE WE
SHOULD GO UP HERE?
WE MIGHT BE HEADING INTO A
ROUGH CROWD.
>> DUDE, I’M JOKING.
THE ONLY KIDS WHO SMOKE CIGS
ON ROOFTOPS ARE THE ONES IN SOME
CHEESY-ASS MANGA.
YEAH, BUT WE JUST GONNA GO UP TO
HIM AND SAY, "HEY, ARE YOU IN
THE DOLLARS?"
HE’S NOT GONNA TELL US THE
TRUTH ABOUT SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> YOU JUST LEAVE THAT TO ME.
I’VE GOT A PLAN.
LET’S SEE...
THERE.
>> HE--HE’S SMOKING...
>> WHAT DO YA KNOW, IT’S
TAKIGUCHI.
YO.
>> HEY.
>> HUH.
OH, COOL, YOU’RE WRITING A SONG.
>> UH, YEAH, I AM.
SO WHAT’S GOIN’ ON?
YOU GUYS NEED SOMETHING?
>> I GOT A QUESTION.
>> GO FOR IT.
>> [clears throat]
YOU A MEMBER OF THE DOLLARS OR
NOT?
>> MASAOMI, WHAT ARE YOU--
>> YEAH, I’M IN WITH THEM.
>> AAHH!
>> THOUGHT SO.
IN FACT, I HAD NO DOUBT AT ALL.
SEE? MY INSTINCTS: PERFECT.
OH, THIS GUY HERE’S AN OLD
FRIEND OF MINE.
>> YEAH, I’M MIKADO RYUGAMINE.
>> OH, YOU’RE THAT GUY.
YOU’RE FAMOUS.
>> HUH? I AM?
>> JUST YOUR NAME.
>> OH.
>> WANT SOME?
>> SURE, THANK YOU.
>> HMM?
>> THANKS, MAN.
>> SO, TAKIGUCHI, I GOT A
QUESTION.
>> HMM?
>> WHAT MADE YOU JOIN THE
DOLLARS?
>> HUH?
HMM.
I’M NOT REALLY SURE EXACTLY
WHY I DECIDED TO DO IT.
I THINK IT WAS SIX MONTHS AGO.
I GOT AN EMAIL FROM SOME GUY I
DIDN’T EVEN KNOW.
HE MENTIONED THE DOLLARS AND
SAID THEY DIDN’T HAVE ANY KIND
OF RULES OR CONDITIONS.
MY FIRST THOUGHT WAS, YEAH,
RIGHT.
BUT THEN I THOUGHT, IF THERE
WAS A GROUP LIKE THAT, I’D
WANT TO BE A PART OF IT.
TRUTH IS, LAST THING I WANT IS
TO BE BOSSED AROUND OR VICE
VERSA.
>> SO, WHAT ARE THE DOLLARS
LIKE?
FILL US IN.
>> WELL, GUESS I’D SAY
TRANSPARENT, AS IN NO COLOR.
>> TRANSPARENT?
>> YEAH.
THEY’RE NOT LIKE THE OTHER GUYS.
THE YELLOW SCARVES AND BLUE
SQUARES WERE ALL ABOUT SHOWIN’
YOUR COLORS AND GETTIN’ INTO
TURF WARS, BUT THE DOLLARS
AREN’T INTO THAT.
>> WHO WERE THE BLUE SQUARES?
>> THEY WERE A COLOR GANG THAT
WAS A BIG DEAL WHEN I WAS IN
MIDDLE SCHOOL.
I DON’T KNOW THE DETAILS, BUT
THEY GOT INTO SOME TROUBLE AND
THEN FELL APART.
>> MASAOMI?
>> SO THEN, YOU’RE TELLING US
THAT YOU LIKE THE DOLLARS?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU EVER GET TOGETHER WITH
THE OTHER MEMBERS?
>> WELL, MEMBERS ONLY KNOW EACH
OTHER BY THEIR USERNAMES.
BUT, YEAH, I’VE MET A BUNCH OF
’EM.
EITHER AT WORK OR IN TOWN.
JUST BY ACCIDENT.
IF YOU THINK, "I BET HE’S WITH
THE DOLLARS," TURNS OUT THEY
USUALLY ARE.
>> HOW CAN YOU TELL BY LOOKING
AT THEM?
>> I DON’T KNOW.
IT’S HARD TO EXPLAIN.
JUST ASK ’EM.
I THINK MOST GUYS YOU ASK
WOULD ADMIT IT STRAIGHT UP.
[alarm rings]
WELL, THAT BLOWS.
>> SEE YA, SUCKERS!
>> ONCE I FOUND OUT THAT
TAKIGUCHI WAS PART OF THE
DOLLARS, I SWORE I’D KEEP IT A
SECRET AND NEVER TELL ANYONE.
I DON’T KNOW HIM, BUT I’M
GUESSING HE WOULDN’T WANT
PEOPLE TO MAKE A BIG DEAL OUT
OF IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, CLASS.
>> I FIGURE IF ANYONE WANTS
TO KNOW, THEY CAN ASK HIM.
STAND.
BOW.
>> OKAY, THAT’S IT FOR THE CLASS
REPS MEETING.
>> I WONDER IF MASAOMI’S HALL
MONITOR MEETING IS OVER.
>> HMM.
WELL, IF IT ISN’T, IT SHOULD
BE OVER PRETTY SOON.
[girls giggling]
>> MIKA HARIMA, THE GIRL WHO
WAS STALKING SEIJI YAGIRI, HAS
BEEN MISSING EVEN BEFORE SCHOOL
STARTED.
SO HAVE YOU HEARD ANYTHING NEW
ON YOUR FRIEND MIKA?
>> NO. NOTHING.
>> HEY, MIKADO!
MASAOMI SAID FOR YOU TO GO
HOME WITHOUT HIM.
>> HUH? WHY?
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
>> YEAH, YEAH, THE HALL MONITORS
ARE JUST HAVING A HUGE ARGUMENT
RIGHT NOW.
IT’S ALL GOOD.
SEE YA!
>> WELL, THEN, ARE YOU READY
TO GO?
>> SURE.
>> I WONDER WHAT’S SO
IMPORTANT THAT MASAOMI WOULD
STAY LATE TO ARGUE ABOUT IT.
YOU KNOW, IT’S PROBABLY JUST
LIKE CLOTHES AND...
>> MIKADO!
DON’T SCREW IT UP WITH THAT
FINE CHICA.
AND NEXT TIME YOU HAVE TO
INTRODUCE ME.
PEACE OUT. LATER!
>> UH...
UH, HE MEANT MISS FINECHICA.
IT’S THIS FRENCH GIRL WE MET
AT THAT RUSSIA SUSHI PLACE.
AND UH, SH-SH-SHE’S GOT--GOT
A NOSE RING!
I’M SURE THAT’S WHAT HE’S BEEN
ARGUING ABOUT, WHETHER OR NOT
THEY SHOULD ALLOW NOSE RINGS AT
SCHOOL.
[laughs]
>> YOU KNOW, I’VE KINDA KNOWN
WHO YOU WERE LONG BEFORE YOU
AND I EVEN MET IN CLASS.
>> HUH?
>> WHEN I CAME TO THE SCHOOL TO
REGISTER, I SAW A LIST OF
NAMES ON A DESK AS I WAS
HANDING IN MY PAPERWORK.
I NOTICED ONE OF THE NAMES
RIGHT AWAY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS COOL.
THE GUY WITH THAT NAME WAS
RIGHT NEXT TO ME.
AND THEN NEXT THING I KNOW, HE
AND I ENDED UP BEING CLASS REPS
TOGETHER.
>> WAIT A SECOND!
ISN’T THIS SORT OF LIKE WHAT
HER FRIEND MIKA DID TO THAT
SEIJI GUY?
OH, MAN. IS SHE A STALKER?
HOLD ON, IF SHE’S CUTE, MAYBE
IT’S OKAY.
NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS STILL BAD.
IF SOMETHING HAPPENS...
>> I WANT YOU NOW!
>> SHE COULD TOTALLY STAB ME!
OR SHE MIGHT EVEN SET MY PLACE
ON FIRE!
HOLD ON, WHAT IF SHE TAKES MY
PARENTS HOSTAGE?
BUT IF SHE’S A GOOD PERSON,
MAYBE I DON’T MIND HER STALKING
ME.
WHAT AM I SAYING?
IF SHE’S STALKING ME, THEN SHE
CAN’T BE A GOOD PERSON!
>> I WAS JUST KIDDING.
BESIDES, YOU WOULDN’T WANT
SOMEONE LIKE ME HANGING AROUND
ALL THE TIME.
>> NO, I...
>> I KNOW THAT SOUNDED WEIRD.
BUT DON’T WORRY, I’M NOT A
STALKER OR ANYTHING.
>> NO, I DIDN’T--
WELL, I...
I’M SORRY.
>> HUH. NO, IT’S FINE.
I WAS THE ONE WHO STARTED IT BY
TEASING YOU.
THERE’S NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, LISTEN, I’M--I’M GLAD
WE BECAME FRIENDS.
>> I’M GLAD WE BECAME FRIENDS
TOO.
>> HUH?
>> YEAH, IT’S BEEN A LOT OF FUN.
>> [exclaims]
TAKESHI, THAT’S HIM.
THAT’S THE LOSER. LOOK!
>> HUH?
>> I WONDER WHO THE LOSER IS.
IT’S NOT ME, RIGHT?
>> I’M TALKIN’ TO YOU!
DON’T IGNORE ME, YOU PATHETIC
RUNT.
>> WELL, JUST HOW DO I KNOW YOU?
>> I’M THE ONE WHOSE CELL PHONE
WAS SMASHED BY YOUR FREAKY
FRIEND, SO I HAD TO GO AND BUY A
NEW ONE.
>> SORRY, BUT I REALLY HAVE NO
IDEA WHAT YOU’RE TALKING ABOUT.
OH.
>> [growls]
>> OH...
>> THIS TRUE?
YOU FRIENDS WITH THAT
PUNK-ASS BITCH WHO WENT AND
BUSTED UP MY GIRL’S CELL PHONE?
>> WELL, I DON’T THINK HE
AND I ARE REALLY FRIENDS.
>> SO THEN WHAT IS HE, YOUR
DADDY?
YOUR LEGAL GUARDIAN?
HUH?
>> THOSE REALLY YOUR OTHER
GUESSES?
>> HUH?
YOU TRYING TO GET SAUCY
THERE, RUNTLING, ARE YA?
I THINK IT’S TIME YOU GOT A
LESSON ABOUT WHERE YOU BELONG
ON THE FOOD CHAIN.
HUH?
[groans]
>> [laughing]
ARE YOU EXPLOITING MY RULE
AGAINST HITTING WOMEN?
WHAT A CLEVER GIRL YOU ARE.
I WOULD ASK YOU OUT.
HOWEVER, YOU’RE SO NOT MY TYPE.
NOW SCRAM!
>> YOU’RE AN ASSHOLE!
>> HAVE A NICE DAY!
SO, MIKADO RYUGAMINE...
I WAS LAYING LOW OUTSIDE THE
SCHOOL’S FRONT GATE HOPING I’D
RUN INTO YOU.
I’D LIKE TO HAVE A LITTLE CHAT.
BY THE WAY, WHAT’S THE BLACK
RIDER DOING HERE?
>> IT’S LOOKING FOR THAT GIRL.
OH, GOSH. I FORGOT!
I-I’M SORRY, BUT I REALLY
GOTTA GO RIGHT NOW!
BYE. SEE YOU TOMORROW, ANRI.
>> VROOM. VROOM.
VROOM. VROOM. VROOM.
VROOM.
>> THIS IS SO BIZARRE.
IF THEY STAY ON MY TAIL LIKE
THIS, THEY’RE GONNA END UP
FOLLOWING ME ALL THE WAY HOME.
AND THEN...
>> SAVE ME!
>> UM, OKAY.
SO, IF YOU WANT TO TALK TO ME
ABOUT SOMETHING, LET’S DO IT
NOW.
[cell phone ringing]
>> GO ON, I’LL LET THE
BLACK RIDER GO FIRST.
HELLO? [laughs]
ALWAYS HAPPY TO BE OF SERVICE.
>> UM, THERE’S SOMETHING I WOULD
LIKE TO ASK YOU.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> SO IT CAN COMMUNICATE.
WELL, I-I WAS JUST WONDERING
WHAT YOU ARE.
>> I’M LOOKING FOR A GIRL.
SHE’S A RELATIVE OF MINE WHO’S
GONE MISSING.
I FOUND HER YESTERDAY, BUT THEN
SHE RAN AWAY FOR SOME REASON.
>> IT’S A TERRIBLE LIAR.
UM, I’M SORRY, BUT I DON’T
BELIEVE YOU.
>> HOW MUCH DO YOU REALLY KNOW
ABOUT ME?
>> WELL, I-I JUST KNOW WHAT THE
URBAN LEGEND SAYS--
THAT YOU RIDE AROUND ON THIS
BIKE WITH NO HEADLIGHT AND NO
ACTUAL MOTOR SOUNDS.
AND THAT...
THAT YOU DON’T REALLY HAVE A
HEAD.
>> AND DO YOU ACTUALLY BELIEVE
THIS?
>> YOU KNOW, YOU COULD ALWAYS
SHOW ME WHAT’S INSIDE YOUR
HELMET.
THAT WAS PRETTY SHOCKING,
EVEN FOR ME.
I DIDN’T THINK I’D HAVE THE
GUTS TO SAY THAT.
>> PROMISE ME THAT YOU WON’T
SCREAM?
>> BUT AT THE SAME TIME, I
FELT LIKE I’D BEEN WAITING FOR
A MOMENT LIKE THIS TO OCCUR
FOR YEARS.
I STILL CAN’T DESCRIBE HOW I
FELT AT THAT EXACT MOMENT.
I JUST FOUND MYSELF THINKING,
"I KNEW IT! I KNEW IT!", OVER
AND OVER AGAIN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
AFTER THAT, THE BLACK RIDER
TOLD ME EVERYTHING--LIKE THE
REAL REASON IT WAS LOOKING FOR
THAT GIRL YESTERDAY.
IT TOLD ME IT WAS A DULLAHAN
NAMED CELTY.
THAT SHE’D COME TO JAPAN IN
SEARCH OF HER HEAD THAT HAD BEEN
STOLEN.
AND WHEN CELTY SAW THE GIRL WITH
STITCHES ON HER NECK, HER FACE
LOOKED JUST LIKE HER OWN.
NORMALLY, I WOULD NEVER BELIEVE
A STORY LIKE THAT, BUT FOR
SOME REASON, SITTING THERE WITH
HER, I FELT LIKE I COULD.
>> SO, ARE YOU FRIENDS WITH THIS
GIRL?
>> NO.
ACTUALLY, YESTERDAY WAS THE
FIRST TIME THAT I EVER MET HER.
I ASKED HER A LOT OF
QUESTIONS, BUT SHE TOLD ME
THAT SHE’D LOST ALL HER
MEMORIES AND...
MISS CELTY?
>> WOULD YOU BE WILLING TO LET
ME SEE HER?
>> WELL, I DON’T KNOW.
I MEAN, SHE DOES SEEM PRETTY
FREAKED OUT BY YOU.
YOU DID CHASE HER DOWN KIND
OF HARD YESTERDAY.
>> I NEED TO SEE THIS GIRL, NO
MATTER WHAT.
MAYBE YOU CAN CLEAR UP ANY
FALSE IMPRESSIONS?
>> I’LL DO MY BEST.
>> [gulping]
[sighs]
NOTHIN’ LIKE SOME FRUITY MILK
IN THE AFTERNOON.
>> I DON’T KNOW ABOUT YOU, BUT
FOR ME, THIS IS A SURE SIGN THAT
SHE’S TURNING INTO A REAL
BIRI BIRI HEROINE!
>> NO, NO, NO, THE ONLY REAL
HEROINE IS GONNA BE HIMEGAMI!
>> HMM? HMM.
[tires screeching]
[shouting]
>> CHILL, DUDE.
[screams]
[thud]
WHAT THE HELL’S GOIN’ ON?
>> THAT BASTARD.
WHAT HE DID...
HE KICKED UP A ROCK AND HIT MY
VAN!
[tires screeching]
[exclamations]
>> CALM DOWN, SABURO!
>> YOU WON’T GET AWAY WITH THIS!
>> THAT’S A RED LIGHT.
RED LIGHT! RED LIGHT!
[tires screech]
>> JUST GIVE ME A MINUTE, OKAY?
I WANT TO GO INSIDE AND EXPLAIN
THINGS.
I’M AFRAID SHE MIGHT THINK THAT
I BETRAYED HER IF SHE SEES YOU
GUYS BEFORE I TELL HER WHAT’S
REALLY GOING ON.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> HE SURE IS A CAUTIOUS BOY,
ISN’T HE?
>> HUH?
[groans]
>> YOU KNOW, THIS WAS THE FIRST
TIME I’VE ACTUALLY HEARD YOUR
REAL NAME.
I HAD NO IDEA THAT YOU WERE A
FOREIGNER.
>> LIAR.
THROW ANOTHER ROCK AT MY HORSE,
AND I’LL MAKE YOU SWALLOW IT.
>> WOW. IT’S A HORSE.
WHO KNEW?
HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THIS IS TAKING LONGER THAN IT
SHOULD, RIGHT?
>> CLEANING SERVICE?
IN THIS RUNDOWN PLACE?
[gasps] OH, NO.
>> [moans]
>> ALL RIGHT, I’M GONNA MAKE
THIS REAL EASY FOR YA.
ALL YA GOTTA DO IS TELL US
WHERE YOU’RE HIDING THE GIRL.
>> THIS HAIR THAT I FOUND IN
YOUR FUTON LOOKS TO ME LIKE A
GIRL’S HAIR.
>> PLEASE! I REALLY DON’T KNOW!
JUST--JUST LET ME GO, OKAY?
>> WE CAN’T DO THAT NOW THAT
YOU’VE SEEN OUR FACES.
BEST THING FOR US TO DO WOULD
BE TO KILL YOU RIGHT HERE.
>> SOMEONE’S COMING.
>> OH, THANK GOD, I’M SAVED.
>> THERE’S NO NEED TO FOLLOW
THEM.
I KNOW WHERE THEY’RE FROM.
I’VE SEEN THAT VAN BEFORE.
CHANCES ARE PRETTY GOOD YAGIRI
PHARMACEUTICALS SENT THEM.
>> A PHARMACEUTICAL COMPANY?
>> YEP.
IT’S A DYING BEHEMOTH OF A
COMPANY THAT’S ABOUT TO BE
BOUGHT OUT BY A FOREIGN
INVESTOR.
>> THE GIRL WITH THE SCAR ON
HER NECK...
THE DULLAHAN...
THE DISAPPEARANCES...
MIKA HARIMA...
SEIJI YAGIRI...
HUMAN TRAFFICKING...
AND THEN THE DOLLARS.
>> WHAT’S HE DOING?
>> I DIDN’T WANT TO BE NORMAL.
>> HONESTLY, I ONLY HALF
BELIEVED THIS WAS TRUE.
>> I NEED A BIG FAVOR.
I’M HOPING YOU GUYS CAN HELP ME
OUT.
I WANTED MY LIFE TO BE
DIFFERENT FROM EVERYONE ELSE.
ALL RIGHT, I THINK ALL MY CARDS
ARE IN ORDER NOW.
>> [laughs]
>> THAT’S WHY...
>> AND JACKPOT.
>> I DECIDED TO.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> I DIDN’T WANT TO BE NORMAL.
I WANTED MY LIFE TO BE DIFFERENT
FROM EVERYONE ELSE, BUT I NEVER
WOULD HAVE THOUGHT THAT THIS ONE
SIMPLE WISH WOULD AFFECT SO MANY
PEOPLE.
NEXT TIME, STORM AND STRESS.