[Complication
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK’D]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> I WAS WONDERING
IS IT REALLY OKAY FOR THE
DOLLARS TO EXIST?
>> I MUST--I MUST TAKE CARE OF
THIS.
>> AND REGARDLESS OF WHAT YOU
LEARN ABOUT HER, NEVER LOOK
AWAY.
>> THIS IS THE VERY DEFINITION
OF CHAOS.
>> SHE HAD ON A RAIRA UNIFORM.
AND I REMEMBER, LIKE, A SERIOUS
SET OF HOOTERS ON HER.
>> NO WAY.
IT’S IMPOSSIBLE.
THIS IS ANRI.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> [chuckles]
>> THE YELLOW SCARVES JUST
SURROUNDED SOME GIRL.
>> WHERE?
>> THEY’RE RIGHT BEHIND CITY
HALL.
OH, WAIT, THEY’RE MOVING.
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY’RE TAKING HER
SOMEWHERE.
>> WHAT’S SHE WEARING?
>> I THINK IT’S A RAIRA
UNIFORM.
>> OKAY, SHE’S A RAIRA STUDENT
WITH GLASSES AND BIG BOOBS.
>> WHAT’S GOING ON?
WHY IS IT THAT ANRI...
>> [grunts]
[door slams]
>> EVERYONE IN THE DOLLARS,
EMERGENCY!
>> YEAH, LET’S ALL SAVE HER.
>> I AIN’T GONNA LET THOSE
PRICKS GET AWAY WITH THIS.
>> THE YELLOW SCARVES HAVE GONE
TOO FAR.
>> [laughing]
ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
I’LL ENJOY THE REST FROM THE
COMFORT OF MY LIVING ROOM.
>> [gasping]
>> IF ANYONE’S CLOSE TO HER,
HELP HER!
EVERYONE ELSE, GET OVER THERE.
[Yellow Scarves chuckling]
>> WELL, WELL, WELL.
WHAT HAVE WE HERE?
SO THEN.
YOU WITH THE DOLLARS?
YOU WERE THE ONE WHO CAME TO OUR
HIDEOUT WITH THE BLACK RIDER.
RIGHT?
YOU LITTLE BITCH.
>> THESE GUYS MUST BE PART
OF THE YELLOW SCARVES.
>> OFFICER!
OVER HERE!
QUICKLY, HELP!
>> HUH!
HEY, GET BACK HERE!
>> THIS WAY.
>> WHAT WAS I DOING?
WHAT WAS IT ALL FOR?
[gasping]
HUH?
>> THIS WAY.
>> OH.
>> YOU GO STRAIGHT HERE.
YOU FIND EXIT IN BACK.
>> I FELT COMPELLED TO DO
SOMETHING, ANYTHING.
>> WHERE THE HELL DID SHE GO?
>> I FOUND THE GIRL.
I HELP HER THROUGH BACK OF ORB
EE-KAY-BOO-KOO-ROH BUILDING.
BUT THEY STILL CHASE HER.
>> THE ORB BUILDING!
IS ANYONE NEAR THERE?
>> BUT IT SEEMS BEING CONFUSED
AND RUNNING FROM THINGS
IS WHAT I ALWAYS DO.
HUH?
>> YOU-A NO PANIC.
GET THAT-A YOUR EXIT.
>> HUH?
>> EASY AS A PIECE OF PIE IN
YOUR EYE.
>> WHY?
>> [chuckles]
>> PUSH-A DE BUTTON.
>> HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY!
WHA!
>> WAIT, WAIT!
[panting]
>> HEY, HORADA, DON’T LEAVE US!
>> I-A GOURD--UH, GUARD AT THE
ORB BUILDING AND IT’S A DOLLARS,
SO I SAVE HER.
>> OH.
[phone beeps]
>> SHE’S BEHIND THE ORB
BUILDING?
THAT’S RIGHT BY WHERE I WORK.
I’LL HOP ON OVER.
>> [gasping]
DAMN IT.
>> OH!
HUH?
OOH, OOH!
AHH!
>> HUH?
>> WHO ARE YOU?
AND...
WHY ARE YOU HELPING ME?
>> [gasping]
SON OF A...
UGH.
AGH!
OW.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> HEY, UH, I’M A DOLLAR THAT
JUST HAPPENED TO BE PASSING BY,
SO I THOUGHT I’D HELP OUT.
I WAS ACTUALLY THINKING OF
QUITTING, BUT...
>> YOU CAN’T QUIT.
STAY WITH US!
>> I KNEW YOU’D COME BACK.
>> IS THIS A DREAM?
[phone beeping]
>> ANYONE KNOW WHERE THE GIRL IS
NOW?
>> IS THAT IT?
AM I DREAMING?
>> [grunts]
MOVE IT!
UGH.
HUH?
>> HEH, HEH.
THE GIRL HAS JUST TRANSFORMED
INTO A GIANT BUNNY.
>> DAMN IT, DUDE.
WHERE’D SHE GO?
>> I DON’T KNOW.
>> YOU LITTLE PIECE OF--
>> THE MORE YOU TALK TO ME,
THE FARTHER AWAY SHE GETS.
>> ASSHOLE.
[groans]
YOU IDIOTS!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> HEY.
WHAT THE HELL’S GOING ON?
>> WHADDAYA THINK?
THE DOLLARS ARE SCREWING WITH
US!
GET SOME BACKUP.
WE’LL FIGHT THEIR STUPID NUMBERS
WITH MORE NUMBERS.
>> PEOPLE I’VE NEVER MET ARE
GOING OUT OF THEIR WAY TO HELP
ME.
I FEEL LIKE I’M DREAMING ALL
OF THIS.
>> [gasping]
>> THIS WAY!
[tires squealing]
>> THE BUNNY IS NOW ACROSS THE
ROAD.
>> SABURO, PUNCH IT.
>> ON IT.
[tires squeal]
>> men: HUH?
>> FIGHTING IS ALWAYS BAD.
YOU WILL BECOME SUSHI NOW.
[phones beeping]
[engine approaching]
>> OH!
WOW, LOOK AT ’EM ALL RING.
>> IT’S NOT COMING JUST FROM OUR
SIDE, THOUGH.
IT’S THEIRS, TOO.
>> HUH? A BUNNY?
>> A BUNNY WITH HUGE BOOBS?
[indistinct chatter]
[phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
>> YEAH, THAT’S RIGHT.
A BUNNY.
[phone ringing]
>> DOES ANYONE KNOW WHERE THE
BUNNY COSTUME WENT?
IF ANYONE’S SEEN HER, LET ME
KNOW.
>> [panting]
OH.
>> THAT HER?
>> I DON’T KNOW.
IT’S HARD TO SEE HOW BIG HER
BOOBS ARE.
>> GUESS WE’LL JUST HAVE TO
STRIP HER, THEN.
>> OH.
BUT...
>> HEY THERE, LITTLE RABBIT.
>> MY DREAMS ARE ALWAYS
JUST LIES THAT I TELL MYSELF.
[whimpering]
[thump]
>> GET HER!
>> WHAT THE--
>> THE ONLY THING I EVER DREAMED
OF WAS A HAPPY, LOVING FAMILY.
SO THEN THIS CAN’T BE A DREAM.
IT HAS TO BE REAL.
HIS HAND IS TELLING ME IT’S
REAL.
AND THEN I SUDDENLY REALIZED...
THAT I KNEW THIS HAND...
ALTHOUGH I’D NEVER TOUCHED HIM
BEFORE.
THIS IS...
>> [gasping]
>> WAIT.
WAIT!
[gasping]
HOW COME YOU NEVER REALIZE
WHAT’S IMPORTANT TO YOU
UNTIL AFTER IT’S ALREADY GONE?
MASAOMI...
WHY?
>> YOU’RE ASKING WHY?
WHY I’D SAVE YOU FROM THE YELLOW
SCARVES, SINCE I’M ACTUALLY
PART OF THAT GANG?
>> UH--
>> THAT’S MY BOOBYLICIOUS ANRI
FOR YA!
EVEN A BUNNY SUIT LOOKS GOOD
ON YOU.
HEY, CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
WERE YOU THERE TO SPY ON US?
IS THAT WHY YOU CAME THERE?
TELL ME, ANRI.
WHAT ARE YOU AFTER?
>> UH...
I WAS JUST--
BECAUSE YOU--
[sighs]
>> ’CAUSE I WHAT?
WHAT DID I DO?
AM I AN IDIOT FOR SAVING YOU?
GUESS I AM.
>> NO, YOU’RE NOT.
DON’T SAY THAT.
>> DOES MIKADO KNOW ANYTHING?
>> UH--
>> JUST WHAT WERE YOU PLANNING
TO DO ABOUT HIM?
>> I WAS JUST--
>> HOW COULD YOU?
>> [gasping]
UH.
>> YOU KNOW HOW HE FEELS ABOUT
YOU!
>> WHY DON’T YOU TELL HIM THE
TRUTH ABOUT WHAT YOU’VE BEEN
DOING?
>> WAS IT FUN LEADING ME ON
WHILE YOU WERE CUDDLING UP
WITH HIM?
OH!
>> [whimpering]
>> [grunts]
WHAT THE HELL AM I DOING?
DAMN IT.
[thunder rumbles]
[phone ringing]
[wind whistling]
>> [gasping]
>> IT’S JUST THAT...
I DIDN’T WANT YOU TO GET HURT.
OR WORSE, HAVE YOU DO SOMETHING
THAT WOULD GET SOMEONE HURT.
SO I CHOSE TO RUN AWAY FROM YOU,
TOO.
I JUST...
[footsteps approach]
>> THERE!
>> GET HER!
>> ALL RIGHT.
[Yellow Scarves chuckling]
>> COME CLEAN.
YOU’RE WITH THE DOLLARS, AIN’T
YA?
>> I’M NOT.
>> HA!
DON’T YOU LIE TO ME.
IF YOU AIN’T WITH THEM,
THEN YOU BETTER START TALKING
AND TELL ME WHO THE HELL YOU
ARE!
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU REALLY WANT TO HEAR
THE TRUTH ABOUT WHO I AM?
>> HUH?
COME ON.
WE’RE WAITING.
GO ON.
WHO ARE YOU REALLY?
[Yellow Scarves chuckle]
OH, I KNOW WHAT IT IS.
YOU’RE A SUPERHERO, AREN’T YA?
YOU WANT PEACE AND MADE OUR
FRIENDS DEFENDERS OF JUSTICE.
SEE, WE DID A LITTLE SOMETHING
SPECIAL TO THOSE GUYS.
WISH I COULD SHOW YA.
ISN’T THAT RIGHT?
[Yellow Scarves laugh and agree]
WE BEAT THE LIVING SHIT OUT OF
THEM.
>> WHAT HAVE I--
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
>> SO I DON’T THINK IT’S FAIR
FOR YOU TO WALK AWAY
WITHOUT A SCRATCH.
UH...
[phone beeps]
HUH?
>> SHUT THE HELL UP.
STOP FREAKIN’ BEEPING AT ME.
I CAN’T READ ALL THIS CRAP.
GIRLS WITH BIG BOOBS, BUNNY
SUITS.
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT ME TO
DO?
SCREW THIS.
HUH.
HUH?
>> UH...
>> HUH?
>> IT’S OKAY.
I FOUND THE GIRL.
SHE’S FINE.
IT’S ALL SETTLED.
[bang!]
>> [screaming]
>> BECAUSE...
>> [gasping]
>> [screaming]
>> BECAUSE...
>> THE FORTISSIMO OF IKEBUKURO
IS HERE!
>> [grunting]
>> [screaming]
[crash!]
>> [growling]
[Yellow Scarves screaming]
>> UM...
I JUST WANTED TO THANK YOU
FOR SAVING ME ONCE MORE.
>> WHO ARE YOU AGAIN?
HEY.
I’M TURNING OFF MY PHONE, OKAY?
CATCH YA LATER.
>> CELTY, I...
[sighs]
>> MISSION COMPLETE.
>> GO DOLLARS!
>> WE DID IT! WE DID IT!
>> ’CAUSE WE’RE THE DOLLARS!
>> WHEN WE WORK TOGETHER, WE
TOTALLY ROCK.
>> THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
I FIGURED IT OUT.
I’VE FINALLY FOUND THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING OF ALL.
>> MIKADO?
>> OH, NO.
IS THE MATCH OVER ALREADY?
AH, SHIZUO-CHAN ALWAYS SHOWS UP
AT JUST THE RIGHT TIME.
HOWEVER, THIS ISN’T FINISHED
YET.
WITH A BIT MORE TIME, I’LL BE
ABLE TO PIN EVERYONE INTO BOTH
CHECK AND CHECKMATE.
>> [grunting]
HUH.
HUH?
>> OH, THERE IT IS.
CELTY, GET THE MUSHROOM.
[video game music]
[laughing] COME ON, CELTY.
THAT MOVE WILL NEVER WORK.
IT’S IMPOSSIBLE.
I TOLD YOU BEFORE, YOU GOTTA
BE CAREFUL AROUND THERE.
WELL--
HEY, NO, NO, NOT THE--
OH.
CELTY.
>> UH, UM, SORRY FOR BOTHERING
YOU.
>> HM.
>> OH.
>> YOU WERE SLEEPING SO WELL,
I DIDN’T WANT TO WAKE YOU.
>> I’M SORRY FOR BEING SO MUCH
TROUBLE.
>> YOU’RE NO TROUBLE AT ALL.
YOU SHOULD STAY HERE FOR A
WHILE.
IT’S NOT SAFE LIVING ALONE.
>> MM-HMM, MM-HMM.
>> YOU SURE YOU DON’T MIND?
>> LOOK, IF YOU NEED ANYTHING,
I CAN GO GET IT.
>> WELL, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> YOU’RE GONNA STAY HOME FROM
SCHOOL TODAY, RIGHT?
I TOLD MIKADO YOU PROBABLY
WOULD.
>> YOU TALKED TO MIKADO?
DO YOU KNOW HIM?
>> OH.
Y-YEAH, SORT OF.
>> I HAD NO IDEA.
>> LISTEN, ANRI, THERE’S NOTHING
FOR YOU TO WORRY ABOUT.
IT’S ALL GOOD.
I’M ON YOUR SIDE, OKAY?
AND THE WEIRD GUY IN THE WHITE
LAB COAT, YOU CAN TRUST--
>> HMM.
>> WELL, HE’S ON OUR SIDE, TOO.
>> HEY, WHAT WAS THAT?
YOU WERE ABOUT TO SAY SHE CAN
TRUST ME, BUT THEN YOU WENT AND
ERASED IT.
WHY’D YOU DO THAT?
HUH?
COME ON, TELL ME.
WHY?
>> YOU KNOW, I’M A LITTLE
SURPRISED.
>> HUH? BY WHAT?
>> WELL, IT’S JUST THAT I DIDN’T
THINK CELTY WOULD BE LIVING
WITH A GUY.
>> HUH?
[laughs sheepishly]
[thunder rumbles]
[rain pattering on roof]
>> HEY, OUR BOSS HAS BEEN OUT
FOR A WHILE.
>> WHO CARES WHAT HE DOES NOW,
ANYWAY?
YOU GUYS KNOW WHAT WE HAVE TO DO
NEXT.
ALL RIGHT, WE’RE ALL ON THE
SAME PAGE HERE.
EVERYONE HERE KNOWS WHAT OUR
NEXT STEP IS, RIGHT?
WE FIND THE FREAKIN’ DOLLARS
AND BEAT THE SHIT OUT OF ’EM!
[all cheering]
>> [chuckling]
[menacing music]
[thudding and pounding]
>> I’M CALLING THE COPS.
>> [grunting and groaning]
>> WHERE ARE YOU RIGHT NOW?
>> THE YELLOW SCARVES ARE AT IT
AGAIN.
>> THEY’RE GETTING REALLY BOLD.
>> THEY TOTALLY MESSED THIS GUY
UP.
A FRIEND OF MINE SAW IT.
>> DON’T GIVE UP ON THE HOPE.
IF WE ALL WORK TOGETHER LIKE
LAST TIME...
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING
AT THIS VERY SECOND?
>> THE DOLLARS...
WILL DISAPPEAR.
>> HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> THAT THE GUY WHO STARTED
THE GANG?
>> IS THE LEADER RUNNING AWAY?
>> IS HE REALLY GONNA END IT?
>> WELL, AS OF 9:34 P.M....
THE IKEBUKURO DOLLARS WERE
DISBANDED.
HUH.
>> YOU’RE WRONG.
IF WE DISAPPEAR, THAT JUST MEANS
WE’RE GOING BACK TO BEING
COLORLESS, INVISIBLE.
>> THE BOSS CAN’T BAIL NOW.
>> I SAY WE STILL GOTTA BELIEVE.
>> SAY SOMETHING.
>> WHY YOU DO THIS?
>> THE DOLLARS WILL DISAPPEAR.
>> YOU SUCK.
>> HUH?
I CAN’T LOG ON ANYMORE.
>> NO! SERIOUSLY?
AW.
>> I STILL SEE THE HOME PAGE
THERE, BUT THE FORUM WHERE
EVERYONE HOOKED UP IS COMPLETELY
GONE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK’S GOING ON?
>> I GUESS THAT HE REALLY MEANT
IT.
>> THAT’S ENOUGH.
IT’S OVER.
>> MY TIME ALONE FELT VERY LONG.
BUT IT GAVE ME TIME TO REALLY
THINK.
AND THEN, AFTER A WHILE,
I BEGAN TO SEE THEIR FACES.
THEIR SMILES.
IT WAS SO CLEAR.
THEY WOULDN’T GO AWAY.
CELTY, DO YOU HAVE TIME FOR US
TO TALK?
>> OF COURSE.
ACTUALLY, I WANTED TO TALK WITH
YOU, TOO.
>> I FEEL LIKE SINCE YOU KNOW
THE WHOLE TRUTH ABOUT ME, THAT I
CAN TELL YOU EVERYTHING.
>> I SEE.
I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND.
SO THEN I’M GUESSING NEITHER
OF THEM KNOWS WHO YOU REALLY
ARE.
>> THEY HAVE ALWAYS BEEN THERE
FOR ME, NO MATTER WHAT--
BOTH MIKADO AND MASAOMI, TOO.
BUT I NEVER ONCE TOLD THEM.
>> LISTEN, FIRST WE HAVE TO STOP
THIS GANG WAR.
>> YOU’RE RIGHT.
>> SO IN ORDER TO DO THAT,
WE HAVE TO TALK TO MIKADO.
>> UM...
WHY WOULD WE TALK TO HIM?
>> ANRI, HOW MUCH DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT MIKADO?
>> HUH?
>> YOU CLEARLY DON’T KNOW.
HE’S A LOT LIKE YOU.
AND THE REASON HE’S KEEPING
SOMETHING IMPORTANT FROM YOU
IS PROBABLY ’CAUSE YOU MEAN SO
MUCH TO HIM.
BUT HE SHOULD BE THE ONE TO TELL
YOU, NOT ME.
LET ME GO GET HIM.
DON’T FILL HER HEAD FULL OF ANY
STRANGE IDEAS WHILE I’M GONE.
AND DON’T ASK HER QUESTIONS OR
TO BE PART OF ANY WEIRD
EXPERIMENTS.
>> I PROMISE.
TRUST ME FOR ONCE.
>> OKAY, I WILL.
DON’T WORRY, ANRI.
I’LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> CELTY...
I’M DONE.
I DON’T WANT TO RUN ANYMORE.
[phone vibrating]
[gunshots]
>> [grunts]
[men babbling]
>> OH, SHIT, SHIT.
>> COME ON, LET’S GO!
[all screaming]
>> AND DON’T BLAME ME!
MASAOMI KIDA’S THE ONE WHO
ORDERED THIS HIT.
>> [exhales]
[groans softly]
[phone vibrating]
[Butterfly by ON/OFF]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> WHY COULDN’T I MOVE?
WHY’D I HESITATE BACK THEN?
WHAT WAS I SO AFRAID OF?
SAKI, I’M NOT SCARED ANYMORE.
I WON’T RUN AGAIN.
NEXT TIME, COMPLICATED AND
CONFUSED.