[Complication
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK’D]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> BY THE WAY, MR. NIEKAWA,
HOW’S THAT DAUGHTER OF YOURS
DOING?
>> SO THEN YOU KNOW NIEKAWA.
>> OH, JUST HER NAME.
>> WHO’S HARUNA NIEKAWA?
>> THAT’S RIDICULOUS.
SHIZUO’S WAY STRONGER THAN I AM.
>> THIS IS THE PERSON THAT’S
BEEN TROLLING OUR FORUM FOR,
LIKE, THE PAST SIX MONTHS,
RIGHT?
>> RUN!
>> I LOVE YOU SO, SO, SO, SO,
SO, SO MUCH, SHIZUO.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> [pants maniacally]
>> HUH.
KYOHEI,
I’M BORROWING YOUR DOOR.
[grunts with effort]
>> both: WHOA!
>> [sighs]
>> [groans and wails]
>> UGH!
[charging yell]
AH!
>> [whimpers]
>> all: [gasp]
>> SO WHO DO I GET TO BUY ME A
NEW DOOR?
>> WHEN I GOT BACK, I TOLD
SHINRA WHAT HAD HAPPENED...
THAT IT WAS ALL OVER NOW.
>> BUT IT WASN’T OVER.
IN FACT, IT WAS JUST BEGINNING.
>> IT WAS A VERY LONG NIGHT.
THE GUY WHO ATTACKED US WAS
STILL OUT COLD, SO I LEFT HIM
WITH KYOHEI AND THE OTHERS
WHILE I TOOK THE GIRL HOME.
>> [sniffs]
>> THIS IS THE GIRL WHO HANGS
OUT WITH MIKADO.
BEFORE WE LEFT, SHE ASKED TO SEE
IF I REALLY DIDN’T HAVE A HEAD.
>> SO YOU SHOWED HER?
>> YES, AND LIKE MIKADO, SHE
WASN’T SURPRISED.
MAYBE THAT’S JUST HOW KIDS ARE
THESE DAYS.
>> DOUBT IT.
I DON’T THINK BEING A KID HAS
ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT.
[doorbell rings]
>> [starts] HUH?
>> IS THAT CELTY?
[doorbell rings]
>> [starts]
HUH?
UM, EXCUSE ME, BUT WHO ARE YOU?
>> GOOD EVENING, ANRI.
MY NAME’S HARUNA NIEKAWA.
>> SO THAT’S IT.
THAT’S ALL THAT HAPPENED.
THANKS FOR LOOKING INTO SAIKA,
BUT I THINK IT’S OVER NOW.
>> YEAH, MAYBE, BUT YOU KNOW,
IT SEEMS A LITTLE TOO
ANTI-CLIMACTIC FOR ME, TOO EASY.
>> SO WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO
WITH THIS GUY?
>> WELL, WE SHOULD CALL AN
AMBULANCE, I GUESS.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
>> all: HUH?
>> [inhales]
SOMETHING JUST DOESN’T FEEL
RIGHT TO ME.
WHY IS THAT?
I’M OFF TO SHINJUKU TO KILL
IZAYA.
I’LL BE BACK.
>> OH, MAN, THIS IS SO COOL!
SHIZU-CHAN TOTALLY HAS THE HOTS
FOR IZAYA.
>> all: HUH?
>> BOY-ON-BOY LOVE IS SO MUCH
FUN.
I LOVE IT!
>> all: NOT HAPPENIN’.
>> HUH?
>> YOU KNOW, SHE MIGHT BE--
>> NO, JUST THE THOUGHT OF THOSE
TWO TOGETHER IS WRONG.
>> HMM.
>> ANYWAY, HERE IT IS.
JUST DON’T TOUCH IT.
IT MIGHT POSSESS YOU.
>> HMM.
[otherworldly unraveling]
>> THIS IS SAIKA?
A BUTCHER KNIFE?
>> IT SURPRISED ME, TOO, BUT
THE GUY HOLDING IT HAD THE
GLOWING, RED EYES AND A
HIGH-PITCHED VOICE.
HE SOUNDED LIKE A WOMAN, AND HE
KEPT SPOUTING CRAZY NONSENSE
ABOUT LOVE OR SOMETHING.
>> WELL, NOW.
LOVE, HUH?
>> I FEEL LIKE I’VE SEEN THAT
GUY SOMEWHERE BEFORE.
REGARDLESS, HOW DOES LOVE HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO WITH SLASHING?
IS SAIKA SOME KIND OF SADIST?
>> NO, I DON’T THINK SADIST IS
THE WORD YOU’RE LOOKING FOR.
AHEM.
SEE, SAIKA’S DESIRE IS
ULTIMATELY TO LOVE PEOPLE.
THAT BLADE HAS BEEN INFATUATED
WITH THE HUMAN RACE FOR SO LONG
THAT IT STOPPED SEEING PEOPLE AS
INDIVIDUALS, AND NOW IT’S
OBSESSED WITH HUMANITY...
ALL OF HUMANITY.
>> I DON’T UNDERSTAND.
IF IT LOVES PEOPLE, WHY SLASH
THEM?
>> [uncomfortable sigh]
>> SO ANRI...
>> [whimpers]
>> I DECIDED TO COME HERE AND
PAY YOU A VISIT TONIGHT.
KNOW WHY?
>> IS IT BECAUSE OF THAT
TEACHER, MR. NASUJIMA?
I DON’T KNOW WHAT YOU’VE HEARD,
BUT I’VE HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
HIM.
THOSE ARE JUST RUMORS PEOPLE ARE
SPREADING.
>> OH, I KNOW THAT.
>> [sighs]
>> BUT YOU SEE, I LOVE TAKASHI.
>> HUH?
>> WHEN PEOPLE ARE IN LOVE, THEY
HAVE VARIOUS WAYS IN WHICH THEY
TRY TO EXPRESS THAT EMOTION,
RIGHT?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> LIKE HOLDING HANDS, OR
EMBRACING, OR EVEN TALKING.
>> SO THE TWO OF YOU WERE
DATING, THEN?
>> IT WAS MORE THAN JUST SIMPLE
DATING.
THE TWO OF US WERE IN LOVE,
AND KNOWING THAT WAS ALL THE
HAPPINESS BOTH OF US EVER
NEEDED.
YES, WE WERE GONNA BE TOGETHER
FOREVER...
BUT THEN ONE DAY HE REJECTED ME.
I DON’T KNOW WHY.
I JUST WANTED TO SHOW HIM I
REALLY LOVE HIM.
>> MM.
SO THEN, WHAT DID YOU DO TO
PROVE IT TO HIM?
[gulps]
>> AT SOME POINT, SAIKA BEGAN
WANTING TO EXPRESS ITS LOVE
THROUGH ACTIONS, BUT SAIKA’S
JUST A SWORD; IT HAS NO BODY.
>> SO IT USES THE BODY OF
WHOEVER’S POSSESSING IT.
>> AND THEN IT STARTS SLASHING
PEOPLE, OVER AND OVER AGAIN,
TRYING TO ILLUSTRATE WHAT IT
FEELS.
>> IT WANTS ITS LOVE TO HAVE
TANGIBLE FORM.
>> TAKASHI SPURNED MY LOVE.
THAT’S FINE, REALLY, I DON’T
HATE HIM FOR THAT.
YOU SEE, THERE’S NO WAY I COULD
EVER HATE HIM, BECAUSE I TRULY
LOVE HIM.
>> OKAY, WELL, THEN--
>> EVEN IF HE NEVER COMES BACK
TO ME, IF HE CHOOSES SOMEONE
ELSE, THAT’S FINE.
I’LL FORGIVE HIM.
HOWEVER...
>> [whimpers]
>> IF SOMEONE TAKES TAKASHI’S
LOVE, I WON’T FORGIVE THEM, NOT
EVER.
>> [whimpers]
>> ABOUT FIVE YEARS AGO, SAIKA
SEEMED TO HAVE DISAPPEARED, BUT
FROM WHAT I’VE SEEN IN THAT CHAT
ROOM, I’D SAY THAT BLADE IS
STILL VERY MUCH ALIVE, AND IN
LOVE.
>> WAIT, SHINRA, I REMEMBER NOW.
I KNEW I’D MET THAT GUY WITH THE
KNIFE SOMEWHERE BEFORE.
HE’S A REPORTER.
HIS NAME IS...
>> I’VE LEARNED THAT YOU CAN’T
ALWAYS RELY ON HUMANS.
IT JUST GOES TO SHOW, IF YOU
WANT TO PROVE YOUR LOVE, THEN
YOU SHOULD GO AND DO IT
YOURSELF.
>> [grunts]
>> I MUST SAY, I THOUGHT FOR
SURE MY FATHER WOULD DO A BETTER
JOB THAN THE OTHERS DID, BUT
CLEARLY I WAS WRONG.
SO I’LL DO THE JOB MYSELF.
I WILL TAKE CARE OF THINGS ON MY
OWN...
WITH YOU, MY NEMESIS.
>> SO THAT MAN, HE WAS YOUR
FATHER?
>> [groans]
UGH.
>> THAT WAS SHUJI NIEKAWA.
HE’S THE GUY WHO WAS ATTACKED
RIGHT IN FRONT OF HIS HOUSE.
>> HMM, WHY WOULD IT DO THAT?
UH, WHAT THE--
WHAT?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SO DO YOU FEEL ANYTHING?
DOES IT SEEM LIKE SOMETHING’S
TRYING TO POSSESS YOU?
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
THIS ISN’T SAIKA.
HERE, SEE FOR YOURSELF.
THERE’S NO WAY THAT A LEGENDARY
BLADE WHOSE HISTORY GOES BACK
FOR DECADES WOULD SAY, "MADE IN
2009."
[taps on phone]
>> HOW CAN THAT BE?
LISTEN, I KNOW WHAT I SAW,
BELIEVE ME.
>> I BELIEVE YOU.
I PROMISE, I WOULD NEVER DOUBT
YOU.
MAYBE THIS NIEKAWA GUY STUMBLED
UPON THE SAIKA LEGEND AND TRIED
TO COPY IT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I THINK THE BIGGER ISSUE IS,
IF THIS ISN’T SAIKA--
>> THEN SAIKA’S STILL OUT THERE
SOMEWHERE, WHICH MEANS CHANCES
ARE, IT’S STILL POSSESSING
SOMEONE AND ATTACKING PEOPLE.
>> HOW ABOUT THE CHAT ROOM?
HAS IT BEEN THERE LATELY?
>> BUT I TOLD YOU, I DON’T CARE
ABOUT NASUJIMA, I PROMISE.
>> THAT’S QUITE ALL RIGHT.
I DON’T CARE HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT
HIM.
THAT’S NOT WHY I’M HERE.
I’M HERE BECAUSE I’M DOING WHAT
I HAVE TO DO IN ORDER TO PROVE
MY LOVE.
>> [whimpers]
>> I DON’T LOVE YOU, BUT WHAT I
HAVE IN MY HAND, SHE WILL.
IN FACT, I THINK SAIKA WILL LOVE
YOU TO PIECES.
>> [gasps]
[overlapping voices]
>> HOW DARE THEY HURT MY SISTER.
MY TIMING WAS--CANNOT DEFY
MOTHER’S ORDERS--HOW DARE THEY--
>> I CAN’T BELIEVE IT.
SAIKA’S SPREADING.
>> IF WE LOOK AT THIS LOGICALLY,
THERE’S ONLY ONE POSSIBLE
CONCLUSION...
CELTY, IMAGINE THIS.
WHEN TWO PEOPLE DECIDE THEY LOVE
EACH OTHER, WHAT DO THEY
FREQUENTLY DO NEXT?
>> DO NEXT?
>> [sighs] I DON’T HAVE ANY
IDEA.
ISN’T BEING IN LOVE WITH SOMEONE
ENOUGH?
>> NOT FOR MOST HUMANS.
ONCE THEY KNOW THEY’RE IN LOVE,
THE NEXT THING THEY DO IS TAKE
IT A STEP FURTHER.
THEY PRODUCE A PRODUCT OF THEIR
LOVE.
>> ARE YOU SAYING--
>> I AM.
I THINK SAIKA IS GIVING BIRTH.
SOMEHOW, BY SLASHING PEOPLE,
IT’S IMPREGNATING THEM.
WAIT, BEFORE YOU GO, I THINK YOU
SHOULD TAKE THIS CHAT LOG ALONG
WITH YOU.
YOU’RE TRYING TO FIND SHIZUO,
RIGHT?
>> WHAT UP, IZAYA, BUDDY?
WHY DON’T YOU COME ON OUT AND
PLAY?
HUH?
>> TELL ME, TO WHAT DO I OWE
THIS PLEASURE, SHIZU-CHAN?
>> I’M OBVIOUSLY HERE TO KICK
YOUR SMARMY LITTLE ASS.
>> AND WHY DO I DESERVE TO HAVE
MY ASS KICKED?
>> BECAUSE I’M PISSED OFF.
>> NOW, DON’T YOU THINK THAT
YOU’RE JUST A LITTLE TOO OLD TO
ACT THE PART OF THE PLAYGROUND
BULLY, SHIZU-CHAN?
>> SHUT THE HELL UP!
SO HOW INVOLVED IN THIS ARE YOU?
>> [laughing] I DON’T KNOW WHAT
YOU’RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> YOU’RE IN WITH THE SLASHER,
BUT I WANT TO KNOW HOW DEEP.
>> [laughs]
THAT’S A HORRIBLE ACCUSATION.
>> 99% OF THE TIME, WHENEVER
RANDOM, VIOLENT CRAP HAPPENS, IT
SEEMS YOU’RE SOMEHOW INVOLVED.
>> AND YOU CAN’T HAVE A LITTLE
FAITH IN THAT LAST 1%?
>> GUESS THAT’S A NO.
>> [grunts]
>> BY THE WAY, I DID SOME
RESEARCH ON YOU.
YOUR LIFE IS PRETTY PATHETIC.
>> [whimpers]
>> IT SEEMS AROUND JUNIOR HIGH,
YOU BEGAN TO LATCH ON TO SOME
GIRL BY THE NAME OF MIKA HARIMA,
TRYING TO SEDUCE EVERY GUY YOU
COULD.
OH, YEAH, I ALSO--
>> WHAT CAN I DO?
HOW CAN I GET OUT OF HERE?
>> ...A ROBBER BROKE INTO YOUR
HOUSE, AND KILLED BOTH YOUR
PARENTS.
YOU WERE IN THE SAME ROOM, BUT--
>> SIMPLE.
I SHOULD JUST ACT LIKE I ALWAYS
DO--LIKE THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH ME.
>> WHY WERE YOU THE ONLY ONE WHO
SURVIVED?
[echoing and distant] WAIT, I
KNOW--YOU SEDUCED THE
PERPETRATOR, DIDN’T YOU?
YOU WERE ALREADY A WHORE THEN.
WAS THE THIEF INTO LITTLE GIRLS?
>> YEAH, THAT’S RIGHT.
>> YOU ARE NOTHING BUT A
DISGUSTING LEECH.
WHAT AN EASY TIME YOU HAVE,
SUCKING THE LIFE OUT OF OTHERS.
>> IT’S NOT EASY.
>> HUH?
COME AGAIN?
>> IT’S NOT EASY LIVING LIKE
THIS, ALWAYS NEEDING SOMEONE
ELSE.
I THINK THAT YOU’RE RIGHT.
LEECH IS A PRETTY GOOD WAY TO
DESCRIBE IT.
HOWEVER, YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
I’VE PUT MYSELF THROUGH, JUST SO
I CAN STAY LATCHED ON TO
SOMEONE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
>> [laughs]
DO YOU REALLY EXPECT ME TO
BELIEVE...
YOU HAD TO DO BAD THINGS FOR
TAKASHI TO LIKE YOU?
>> NO.
>> HUH?
NOT FOR MR. NASUJIMA.
HE’S NOT WORTH THE EFFORT.
>> OH.
THAT’S HOW YOU FEEL.
FINE.
NOW DIE!
[door bell]
>> [whimpers]
>> UH, IS THAT A FRIEND?
>> PERFECT.
I’LL TIE UP YOUR LITTLE FRIEND,
AND KILL THEM IN FRONT OF YOU.
AND WHEN I’M FINISHED, I’LL KILL
YOU.
>> [whimpers]
[motorcycle speeds]
>> [grunts]
[groans]
[grunts]
>> SERIOUSLY?
>> [growls]
A-A-AH!
HUH?
[otherworldly tire screech]
>> WELL, NOW.
>> CELTY.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
>> [grunts]
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
IS THIS PART OF YOUR PLAN, TOO?
>> LOOK, IF I KNEW THIS WAS ALL
IT’D TAKE TO GET CELTY TO SHOW
UP ON MY DOORSTEP, THEN TRUST
ME, I WOULD’VE DROPPED A METEOR
ON YOUR HOUSE A LONG TIME AGO.
>> [scoffs]
[otherworldly engine roars]
>> UNBELIEVABLE.
ONE MOMENT HE’S DUMB AS AN OX,
AND THE NEXT, HE’S SHARP AS A
WHIP.
AND IT’S BECAUSE OF THIS VERY
REASON THAT I HATE HIM SO MUCH.
>> [whimpers]
[starts]
>> HARUNA?
>> TAKASHI!
AH!
TAKASHI, MY LOVE, MY LOVE, MY
LOVE, MY LOVE, MY LOVE!
>> [whimpers]
>> OH.
[screams]
>> I’M AFRAID I DON’T HAVE TIME
TO DEAL WITH YOU ANYMORE.
I’LL HAVE EVERYONE ELSE KILL YOU
INSTEAD.
>> EVERYONE?
>> I HOPE THEY DON’T SPEND TOO
MUCH TIME WITH YOU, THOUGH.
THERE’S STILL SOMEONE ELSE FAR
MORE IMPORTANT LEFT.
[laughs]
[footsteps]
>> [starts]
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[trees rustle]
>> I LOVE YOU, SHIZUO.
[overlapping ghostly voices]
>> all: SHIZUO.
>> SO SHINRA,
HOW MANY SAIKAS DO YOU THINK ARE
GONNA SHOW UP AT SOUTH IKEBUKURO
PARK?
>> I DON’T KNOW, BUT LISTEN,
CELTY--ONE OF THEM HAS TO BE THE
ORIGINAL SAIKA.
JUST FIND THAT ONE.
>> I’LL TRY.
THAT’S THE MOTHER, RIGHT?
>> I’VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU,
SHIZUO HEIWAJIMA.
YOU REALLY ARE WONDERFUL, JUST
LIKE MOTHER SAYS.
EVERYONE HERE KNOWS THAT YOU
WERE THE ONE WHO DEFEATED OUR
SISTERS.
GOTTA LOVE THE INTERNET.
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE THE MOTHER
ISN’T HERE.
BUT WHY?
>> AT FIRST IT WAS DIFFICULT FOR
OUR COLLECTIVE CONSCIOUS TO
ADJUST AND LEARN YOUR HUMAN
LANGUAGE, BUT NOW OUR MINDS ARE
JUST AS WELL-FORMED AS OUR
MOTHER’S.
>> NOW COME ON, SHIZUO, PLEASE
SHOW EVERYONE HERE JUST HOW
STRONG YOU ARE.
WE’RE SO LOOKING FORWARD TO
LOVING YOU.
AND NEITHER THAT MONSTER OR THE
COPS HAS ANY CHANCE OF STOPPING
US.
THEY’RE GONNA BE WAY TOO BUSY
FOR THAT.
YOU SEE, THIS KNIFE IS JUST
GETTING STARTED, BECAUSE NOT TOO
FAR FROM HERE, MY SISTERS ARE
OUT MAKING MORE SISTERS, NOW,
HOW MUCH FUN IS THAT?
[eerie warbling]
>> CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
>> WHATEVER YOU’D LIKE.
>> WHY ME?
WHY DO YOU LIKE ME SO MUCH?
>> ’CAUSE YOU’RE SO STRONG.
YOUR STRENGTH LITERALLY HAS NO
BOUNDARIES, AND WE WOULD LIKE IT
FOR OURSELVES.
ALL THE BETTER TO LOVE HUMANITY
WITH.
WE LIKE SOMEONE WITH GOOD GENES
THE SAME WAY THAT YOU HUMANS DO.
COME ON, NOW, LET’S JUST BE
HONEST HERE.
ODDS ARE, A GUY LIKE YOU WILL
NEVER FIND SOMEONE TO LOVE HIM.
EXCEPT US, WE WANT TO LOVE YOU,
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF US.
>> [laughs]
>> SHIZUO, SNAP OUT OF IT!
IF THINGS GET OUT OF CONTROL,
I’LL TAKE CARE OF IT, OKAY?
>> NO, CELTY, THAT LAUGH WAS
REAL.
I’M KINDA GLAD ABOUT THIS.
>> HUH?
>> YOU DON’T HAVE ANY IDEA HOW
MUCH I’VE HATED HAVING THIS
POWER.
I’VE ALWAYS BEEN AFRAID THAT
BECAUSE OF THIS, NOBODY WOULD
EVER WANT ME.
BUT I WAS WRONG.
ALL RIGHT, THEN, HOW MANY WE
GOT?
LET’S JUST CALL IT A LOT.
SO NOW, THIS SHOULD DO IT.
YOU KNOW, I THINK I CAN FULLY
EMBRACE WHO I AM NOW.
FINALLY START LIKING MYSELF.
I’VE HATED THIS POWER SO MUCH,
I’VE WANTED NOTHING MORE THAN TO
BE RID OF IT.
NOW I CAN FINALLY GO ALL OUT.
HEY, BY THE WAY, I JUST WANT TO
MAKE ONE THING CLEAR.
NONE OF YOU ARE MY TYPE.
NEVER HAVE BEEN, AND NEVER WILL
BE.
I HATE YOU GUYS, ALMOST AS MUCH
AS IZAYA.
[charging yell]
>> SHINRA, SOMETHING ELSE STILL
BOTHERS ME.
YOU SAID SAIKA DISAPPEARED FIVE
YEARS AGO, RIGHT?
WHY IS THAT?
WHAT HAPPENED FIVE YEARS AGO?
>> WELL, I HIGHLY DOUBT IT CHOSE
TO TAKE A VACATION.
IT’S POSSIBLE THAT SOMEONE VERY
STRONG CAME IN CONTACT WITH IT
AND HAS SOMEHOW MANAGED TO
SUPPRESS IT.
[pants in fear]
>> WHO WOULD THAT BE?
>> I’VE THOUGHT ABOUT YOU FOR SO
LONG.
I KNOW YOU LOVED ME AS MUCH AS I
LOVED YOU.
YOU SHOWED THAT IN THE WAY YOU
TRIED TO EXTORT MONEY FROM ME,
AND HOW YOU TRIED TO ABANDON ME,
ONCE YOU GOT BORED.
AND NO MATTER WHAT, I ACCEPTED
YOU, I LOVED AND FORGAVE YOU.
>> [whimpers]
>> BUT STILL, THAT JUST WASN’T
ENOUGH.
NO, THAT WASN’T EVEN CLOSE TO
ENTER SAIKA.
SHE STARTED SPEAKING TO ME AND
TELLING ME THINGS.
>> [pants in fear]
>> THINGS LIKE THIS.
AND THAT’S HOW SHE SPEAKS, WITH
ME GIVING HER MORE BLOOD.
SEE?
>> [whimpers]
>> SO WILL YOU TAKE MY LOVE?
I REALLY DO WANT TO GIVE IT TO
YOU.
>> [whimpers]
[terrified gasp]
[whimpers]
[screams]
>> WAIT!
>> OH.
>> [panting] HARUNA...
PLEASE, YOU HAVE TO STOP THIS.
STOP HURTING PEOPLE WITH THAT
KNIFE!
>> HOW DID YOU GET OUT OF THERE
ALIVE?
>> PLEASE STOP.
>> FINE, WHATEVER.
I’M GUESSING THAT SOMEONE CAME
IN AND SAVED YOU AGAIN.
NOW, LISTEN, I REALLY DON’T LIKE
YOU COMING HERE, AND TELLING ME
WHAT I SHOULD DO.
I DON’T NEED ADVICE FROM SOMEONE
SO WEAK, THAT THEY LEECH OFF OF
OTHERS.
>> YOU HAVE IT WRONG.
I DIDN’T DO IT BECAUSE I WAS
WEAK, I HAD OTHER OPTIONS.
I CHOSE THIS LIFE FOR A REASON,
NOT BECAUSE I HAD TO.
>> HUH, SAME THING.
>> YOU CAN’T JUDGE PEOPLE BY HOW
THEY LIVE AND JUST DECIDE IF
THEY’RE WEAK OR STRONG.
>> SO TELL ME SOMETHING--HAVE
YOU EVER ACTUALLY LOVED SOMEONE
BEFORE?
>> [cries]
>> NO, I DON’T THINK YOU HAVE.
SO IT GOES TO SAY, YOU CAN’T
UNDERSTAND ME.
LISTEN CLOSE, I WAS ABLE TO TAKE
OVER SAIKA WITH THE POWER OF MY
LOVE.
THE FIRST TIME SAIKA TOLD ME TO
CUT TAKASHI, I RESISTED WITH
EVERYTHING I HAD.
BUT THEN, AS I LISTENED TO HER
VOICE, I UNDERSTOOD...
AND THAT’S WHY SAIKA AND I HAVE
BECOME THE MOTHER.
WE’RE MAKING AS MANY CHILDREN AS
WE POSSIBLY CAN IN AN EFFORT
TO SPREAD OUR LOVE.
THAT’S RIGHT, LOVE!
SOMEDAY WE WILL LOVE AND
CONTROL THE ENTIRE HUMAN RACE!
[charging yell]
[grunts]
[metallic impact]
>> [grunts with effort]
>> [gasps]
>> YOU’RE RIGHT.
IT’S LIKE YOU SAID.
I CAN’T LOVE ANYONE.
I’VE BEEN TOO SCARED...
EVER SINCE THAT DAY FIVE YEARS
AGO.
AND THAT’S WHY I CHOOSE TO RELY
ON OTHERS.
>> THIS CAN’T BE!
>> YOU WERE ABLE TO MAKE
CHILDREN BY SLASHING OTHERS WITH
THAT BLADE, BUT YOUR SAIKA IS
JUST ANOTHER CHILD, TOO.
THE MOTHER OF ALL THOSE BLADES
IS THIS.
>> [gasps]
>> OH.
>> I AM UNABLE TO LOVE, AND THIS
IS THE REASON...
THAT I MUST RELY ON SAIKA TO
LOVE OTHER PEOPLE FOR ME.
YOU SEE, I TRULY AM HER
PARASITE.
[Butterfly by ON/OFF]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> IT’S A LIE.
IT’S THE TRUTH.
WHEN A HORRIBLE PAST COLLIDES
WITH THE PRESENT, SHE GAINS
UNPARALLELED POWER.
JUST ANOTHER UNPARALLELED DAY.
NEXT TIME, EVERYTHING CHANGES.