[Complication
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK’D]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> I FINALLY FOUND THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING OF ALL.
>> WAS IT FUN LEADING ME ON
WHILE YOU WERE CUDDLING UP WITH
HIM?
>> I’M DONE.
I DON’T WANT TO RUN ANYMORE.
>> YOU CAN’T KEEP RUNNING FROM
YOUR PAST.
THAT’S WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
SOMETHING FROM YOUR PAST HAS YOU
WORRIED, RIGHT?
[gunshots]
>> DON’T BLAME ME!
MASAOMI KIDA’S THE ONE WHO
ORDERED THIS HIT!
>> THE DOLLARS WILL DISAPPEAR.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
[rain falling]
>> RUSSIA SUSHI.
COME TO RUSSIA SUSHI.
IT’S GOOD. IT’S CHEAP.
HOW ABOUT IT, MISTER?
COME INSIDE.
[jazzy piano music]
♪ ♪
[ghostly neighing]
[phone rings]
>> HELLO, RUSSIA SUSHI.
>> I DIDN’T KNOW WHO ELSE I
SHOULD TALK TO ABOUT THIS, SO...
I DECIDED THAT I SHOULD CALL
YOU.
>> HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE I SHOULD
TELL SOMEONE ABOUT THIS, ABOUT
WHAT HE’S PLANNING TO DO.
>> [laughs]
HEY, NAMIE.
WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE THIS IS
CALLED?
ARE WE IN CHECK? CHECKMATE?
HOW ’BOUT JACKPOT?
HEY!
WELL NOW, WHERE’D SHE GO?
>> [no audio]
>> WHAT DO WE DO?
>> THE YELLOW SCARVES ARE STILL
THRASHING ON PEOPLE.
>> AND FROM WHAT I HEARD, THAT
GUY NAMED HORADA IS THE ONE
BEHIND IT ALL.
>> WHAT’S KIDA DOING ABOUT IT?
>> DUNNO.
>> HORADA?
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT
THAT HORADA?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "THAT
HORADA"?
WHICH ONE ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
>> THIS BLOWS.
MY BRAIN IS SWIMMING IN DOUBT
RIGHT NOW.
DOES MIKADO KNOW THE TRUTH AND
HE’S STILL HAVING THE DOLLARS DO
THIS STUFF?
WERE HE AND ANRI WORKING
TOGETHER?
OR WAS SHE JUST USING HIM?
EITHER WAY, THAT’S LOW.
BUT I GUESS WHAT I’M DOING IS
WORSE, DOUBTING THEM LIKE THIS.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
WHERE DO I GO?
THERE’S NO PLACE LEFT FOR ME TO
TURN.
[ghostly neighing]
[knock at door]
>> COME ON IN.
I KNOW WHY YOU CAME HERE.
BUT...I FIGURED THIS WAS THE
ONLY WAY TO END IT.
I THINK I SETTLED THINGS IN A
PRETTY DOLLARS-LIKE WAY.
I MEAN, IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
THE DOLLARS WERE ALWAYS ABOUT
BEING TRANSPARENT TO BEGIN WITH.
SO WE’LL GO BACK TO BEING
INVISIBLE AGAIN.
I’M PRETTY SURE THE SLASHER AND
THE YELLOW SCARVES WILL GO AWAY
NOW.
I’VE COME TO REALIZE WHAT’S
IMPORTANT TO ME. I THINK THIS IS
BEST.
>> I UNDERSTAND. BUT THAT’S NOT
WHY I’M HERE.
[phone rings]
>> WHAT’S GOING ON?
>> HEY, IT’S ME, HORADA.
>> YEAH, WHAT’RE YOU CALLING
FOR?
>> JUST SO YOU KNOW, WE WON’T BE
NEEDING YA ANYMORE.
>> HUH?
>> YOU’VE BEEN FIRED.
YOU’RE NO LONGER THE HEAD
OF THE YELLOW SCARVES.
YOUR ASS IS CANNED.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> MIKADO RYUGAMINE.
THAT’S THE NAME OF YOUR BEST
BUDDY, RIGHT?
>> [gasps]
>> ISN’T THAT SHOCKING?
IT TURNS OUT THAT THE LEADER OF
THE DOLLARS IS BEST FRIENDS WITH
THE HEAD OF OUR OWN GANG.
>> JUST HOLD ON!
WHO TOLD YOU THAT?
>> WHO CARES HOW I FOUND OUT?
BY THE WAY, YOU DID A GOOD JOB
OF TRICKING US THIS WHOLE TIME.
EVERYONE’S STANDING AROUND
COMPLETELY SHOCKED RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
>> GO AFTER THE DOLLARS’ LEADER,
OF COURSE.
THE GUYS CAN’T WAIT TO KICK SOME
ASS.
AND JUST SO YOU KNOW, THERE’S A
HIT OUT ON YOUR HEAD, TOO.
YOU WON’T BE ABLE TO SHOW YOUR
FACE IN IKEBUKURO AGAIN.
BUH-BYE.
>> MIKADO.
>> MIKADO, DO YOU LIKE ANRI
SONOHARA?
IS MASAOMI KIDA STILL YOUR BEST
FRIEND?
>> WHY ARE YOU ASKING THIS?
>> THE PERSON YOU HAVE DIALED IS
OUT OF THE--
>> YOU HAVE REACHED THE
VOICE MAILBOX FOR--
[doorbell rings]
>> COMING.
HUH?
>> YO.
>> GOODNESS GRACIOUS!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW...
I GOT SHOT.
>> HMM...
BOTH YOUR ABDOMEN AND RIGHT LEG
HAVE SUSTAINED SOME SERIOUS
DAMAGE.
MORE IMPORTANTLY, HOW CAN YOU
EVEN STAND UP RIGHT NOW?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, HOW AM I
STANDING?
JUST BECAUSE I AM.
WHY THE HELL ELSE?
>> [gasps]
SHIZUO!
W-WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> HUH?
MAN, THIS SUCKS.
WHO ARE YOU AGAIN?
>> YOU KNOW HER, THAT’S ANRI.
EXCUSE US FOR A MINUTE, ANRI.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
>> AT FIRST, I THOUGHT IT WAS
NOTHING, THAT I’D JUST FALLEN
DOWN ’CAUSE I SLIPPED IN THE
RAIN.
BUT THEN I SAW BLOOD AND
NOTICED IT WAS COMING FROM MY
OWN LEG AND STOMACH.
THEN I REALIZED, HEY, I’D
BEEN SHOT.
I WAS GETTING READY TO KILL THE
GUYS WHO SHOT ME, BUT BEFORE I
COULD GET TO MY FEET, THEY ALL
RAN OFF.
>> PRETTY DUMB, HUH?
>> WANNA LIVE?
>> MY PROFOUND AND SINCERE
APOLOGIES.
>> JUST FIX ME UP ALREADY.
I’VE GOTTA GO FIND THE BASTARDS
WHO DID THIS TO ME AND KILL ’EM.
>> NO, YOU NEED TO REST.
>> [growls]
THEY’RE DEAD!
BOTH THE GUYS WHO SHOT ME AND
THE ASSHOLE WHO ORDERED IT.
MASAOMI KIDA IS ONE DEAD DUDE!
>> [gasps]
>> THE PERSON YOU HAVE DIALED IS
OUT OF THE AREA--
>> I STOPPED BEING SUSPICIOUS OF
MIKADO AND ANRI.
IF THE YELLOW SCARVES DID ATTACK
MIKADO...
OR IF THEY KIDNAPPED ANRI JUST
TO LURE HIM OUT...
[heavy footsteps]
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHY DID I FREEZE UP BACK THEN?
WHAT MADE ME STOP?
WHAT WAS I AFRAID OF?
>> THERE’S JUST NO ESCAPING IT.
YOU CAN RUN FROM IT ALL YOU
WANT, BUT YOUR PAST WILL ALWAYS
FOLLOW YOU.
[clattering]
>> [grunting]
>> THERE’S NO WAY.
YOU’RE WRONG.
>> IT’S ALL TRUE.
>> SO THEN...
DOES THIS MEAN MASAOMI KNOWS THE
TRUTH ABOUT ME?
>> I DON’T KNOW.
BUT WHEN HE WAS SCREAMING AT
ANRI, HE WAS OBVIOUSLY
RATTLED ABOUT SOMETHING.
IT’S POSSIBLE HE DID FIND OUT
THAT YOU’RE THE ONE WHO STARTED
THE DOLLARS.
>> BUT HOW?
WHO WOULD’VE TOLD HIM THAT?
>> THERE’S AN INFORMATION BROKER
I KNOW WHO SEEMS TO LOVE PUTTING
PEOPLE IN THESE KINDS OF
PREDICAMENTS.
>> [gasps]
>> THE DOLLARS ARE YOURS.
YOU STARTED IT.
DO AS YOU WISH WITH IT.
BUT I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT
MAKING THEM DISAPPEAR ISN’T
GOING TO HELP THE THREE OF YOU
AT ALL.
>> I DON’T GET IT.
WHY DID NEITHER OF THEM JUST
TELL ME?
>> WHY DIDN’T YOU TELL THEM?
>> I GUESS...I JUST FIGURED
THAT...THE DOLLARS WERE MY
PROBLEM.
>> THEY FELT THE SAME.
LOOK, WHAT YOU SEE ISN’T ALWAYS
WHAT’S REAL.
EVERYONE HAS SECRETS, THINGS
THEY FEEL THAT THEY CAN’T TELL
OTHERS.
THERE’S NO SUCH THING AS A
NORMAL PERSON.
DON’T BE AFRAID.
JUST GO OUT THERE
AND FACE MASAOMI, ANRI,
AND YOUR OWN PROBLEMS HEAD ON.
IF YOU LOVE HER, TELL HER THE
TRUTH.
TELL HER EVERYTHING.
THIS ISN’T A PROBLEM FOR THE
SLASHER, THE DOLLARS, OR THE
YELLOW SCARVES.
THIS IS A PROBLEM FOR THE THREE
OF YOU TO SOLVE!
[phone rings]
>> HEY, CELTY, I’M RUNNING AFTER
HER NOW, BUT...
[panting]
SHIZUO’S BEEN SHOT SEVERAL TIMES
AND ANRI RAN OUT OF THE
APARTMENT AS SOON AS SHE FOUND
OUT.
WELL, I MEAN, THAT ISN’T WHY SHE
LEFT.
IT SEEMS THAT THE ORDER TO
HIT SHIZUO CAME FROM MASAOMI
KIDA.
I CAN’T KEEP UP.
I’M OUT OF BREATH.
SORRY, THIS CONVERSATION
IS ALL OVER THE PLACE.
A-ANRI’S JUST SO FAST.
SHE’S TOO FAST!
[clattering]
[dial tone]
>> HUH?
>> [panting]
>> HEY, KIDA.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT IS WRONG?
YOUR FACE WEAR DEPRESSION.
IS IT BECAUSE YOU BE HUNGRY?
>> SIMON.
>> YOU NO LOOK SO WELL.
THAT NOT LIKE YOU.
>> HEY, SIMON.
I GIVE YOUR SUSHI FIVE STARS.
HECK, IF I COULD, I’D GIVE YOUR
SUSHI A WHOLE GALAXY WORTH OF
STARS.
RUSSIA SUSHI WILL ALWAYS HAVE A
PLACE IN MY HEART.
>> DO YOU RUN NOW BECAUSE YOU GO
TO FIGHT?
AND ARE YOU GOING NOW TO KILL
OR BE KILLED YOURSELF?
>> W-WHAT DO YA MEAN?
WHY WOULD YOU SUDDENLY SAY
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
YOU A PSYCHIC NOW?
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
DID IZAYA START SOMETHING AGAIN?
>> THAT’S NOT IT AT ALL.
>> KILL OR BE KILLED.
BOTH VERY BAD.
THE PLACE I USED TO LIVE, EVERY
FIGHT HAS A PERSON WHO DIE IN
IT.
LISTEN, I SEE THAT LOOK IN YOUR
EYE.
IT LIKE FACE WHO READY TO DIE.
I KNOW IT.
>> SIMON...
>> NO, THIS IS IKEBUKURO.
IT NOT LIKE MY TOWN.
IT WARM HERE.
PEOPLE GIVE YOU FOOD,
EVEN IF YOU HAVE NO HOME.
AND YOU NO NEED DRINK VODKA SO
THAT YOU NO FREEZE AT NIGHT AND
DIE.
KIDS LIKE YOU, KIDA, THERE NO
REASON FOR YOU TO KILL HERE.
>> I’M SORRY, BUT I HAVE TO GO
NOW.
>> KIDA...
>> SOMEONE...
ANYONE IN THE YELLOW SCARVES!
ANYBODY!
THERE’S NO ONE.
NO ONE’S HERE.
WHICH MEANS...
[eerie whinnying]
>> INTERESTING.
VERY INTERESTING.
THREE BOSOM BUDDIES EACH
PROTECTING THEIR OWN SECRET.
AND NOW WITH A LITTLE HELP FROM
SERENDIPITY AND JUST A FEW EVIL
DEEDS, ALL OF THEM
WILL SOON DISCOVER THE TRUTH
ABOUT THEIR FRIENDS IN
AN ALMOST IDEAL WAY.
GRANTED, THE EVIL DEEDS WERE ALL
MY DOING.
BUT WHAT CHOICE DID I HAVE?
AFTER ALL, THE PAWN I PLACED AS
A MIDDLEMAN WAS A BORING LOSER.
I HAD TO SPICE IT UP A BIT.
PERHAPS I SHOULD HAVE CHOSEN
SOMEONE ELSE FOR THAT ROLE.
NAMIE, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
[chuckles]
>> DON’T YOU ALL EXPECT A BIT
MORE FROM THE YELLOW SCARVES?
COME ON!
WE’RE NOT LIKE THE DOLLARS,
JUST A BUNCH OF RANDOM KIDS
HOOKING UP ON THE INTERNET.
WE’VE GOT A UNIFIED POWER THAT
THEY DON’T.
I KNOW THE LEADER OF THE DOLLARS
RECENTLY SENT OUT AN ORDER THAT
THEY DISBAND, BUT DON’T BUY THAT
CRAP!
THAT IS OBVIOUSLY SOME SORT OF A
TRAP.
LET’S GET THOSE GUYS BEFORE THEY
GET US!
[cheering]
WE TAKE OUT THE DOLLARS, WE’LL
CONTROL NOT JUST IKEBUKURO, BUT
ALL OF TOKYO AS WELL!
THINK ABOUT IT.
IMAGINE WHAT WE COULD DO.
NOT JUST THIS AREA HERE, BUT
EVERY GANG IN THIS WHOLE DAMN
CITY COULD SOON BE TAKING ORDERS
FROM US.
AND WITH THAT FREAKIN’ SHIZUO
HEIWAJIMA OUT OF THE PICTURE,
THE ONLY ONES LEFT IN THE
DOLLARS STILL ACTING TOUGH IS
KADOTA’S GANG.
SO NEXT WE CRUSH THEM, THEN HIT
THEIR LEADER, RYUGAMINE, THEN
THE ONLY THING OUT THERE FOR
ANYONE TO FEAR WILL BE US!
[cheering]
SO COME ON, LET’S GO HIT
IKEBUKURO AND TAKE THIS TOWN!
[cheering]
[chuckles]
>> YOU STILL THINK THAT IT WAS A
GOOD IDEA, GUNNING HIM DOWN LIKE
THAT?
>> TRUST ME, IT WAS THE RIGHT
THING TO DO.
WITH SHIZUO HEIWAJIMA GONE NOW,
WE GOT NOTHING TO BE SCARED OF
ANYMORE.
>> YEAH, BUT IF THE POLICE FIND
OUT, THEY’LL DESTROY US.
>> THEN WE’LL JUST MAKE IT LOOK
LIKE IT WAS THE DOLLARS FIGHTING
AMONGST THEMSELVES.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THAT’S CRAZY, THAT WON’T WORK!
>> STOP YOUR WHININ’.
OF COURSE IT’LL WORK.
I JUST SAID SO!
>> HORADA...
>> I’M TELLIN’ YA, IT’S GONNA
WORK.
IT HAS TO WORK.
[laughs]
[gasping]
THAT THE COPS?
DON’T TELL ME THEY FOUND US OUT
ALREADY!
EH?
WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
[phantom neighing]
>> WELL, HELLO, CELTY.
YOU WANT SUSHI AGAIN?
>> I’M LOOKING FOR MASAOMI KIDA
AND ANRI SONOHARA.
HAVE YOU SEEN THEM?
>> DA, KIDA I DID SEE.
THE FACE HE WORE WAS A VERY
SERIOUS FACE.
FACE FOR FIGHT.
I TRY, BUT HE NO STOP.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHERE HE WAS
GOING?
>> I’VE BEEN AROUND ALL DAY AND
SEE NO GUYS WITH YELLOW.
I THINK MOST LIKELY HE BE WITH
THEM.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
ARE YOU PREPARED FOR WHATEVER
YOU’LL SEE, NO MATTER HOW UGLY?
>> YES.
>> WHAT’S GOING ON HERE?
I DON’T EVEN RECOGNIZE MOST OF
YOU.
NO ONE’S TAKING MY CALLS.
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
>> WELL, YOU SEE...
ALL THE GUYS WHO SEEMED TO BE
AGAINST ME TAKING THE REINS FROM
YOU WERE MYSTERIOUSLY AMBUSHED
LAST NIGHT BY SOME GANG AND ARE
STILL RECOVERING.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
IT WAS SO SCARY!
IT MUST HAVE BEEN THE DOLLARS
WHO DID IT.
THAT’S HOW IT WENT, RIGHT, GUYS?
[laughter]
>> YOU SON OF A--
>> HA! YOU’RE AN IDIOT.
WHY’D YOU EVEN COME HERE
TONIGHT?
LOOK AT YOU!
YOU’RE PATHETIC.
YOU’RE LIKE A FREAKIN’ MOTH
BEING DRAWN TO THE FLAME.
MAYBE I SHOULD PLAY THE SAME
GAME WITH YOU THAT IZUMII DID.
SNAP ONE OF YOUR LITTLE LEGS IN
HALF AND BE ALL LIKE,
"HEY, IT’S POP QUIZ TIME."
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
YOU WERE PART OF THAT?
>> HUH?
>> DID YOU JUST SAY THAT YOU
KNOW IZUMII?
>> HA! I DON’T KNOW WHAT YOU’RE
TALKING ABOUT.
I JUST KNOW EVERYONE HERE’S DONE
A LOT OF BAD THINGS IN THE NAME
OF THE YELLOW SCARVES.
I THINK IT’S TIME WE START GOING
BY A DIFFERENT NAME AND
DIFFERENT COLOR.
YEAH, MAYBE SOMETHING SAD AND
GLOOMY, LIKE THE COLOR OF YOUR
FACE.
>> ARE YOU--NO.
ALL YOU GUYS, HOW COULD YOU?
>> YOU FINALLY FIGURED IT OUT.
WAY TO GO.
EVERYBODY SURROUNDING YOU RIGHT
NOW ARE THE GUYS YOU HATE,
THE BLUE SQUARES.
SEE, WE AIN’T JUST A BUNCH OF
LOSERS KEEPING A DEAD GANG
ALIVE.
NO, WHAT WE ARE IS THE GUYS
WHO’VE EATEN UP THE YELLOW
SCARVES.
IT’S YOUR OWN DAMN FAULT.
ALL WE HAD TO DO WAS TAKE OFF
OUR BLUE AND ASK TO BE A PART OF
YOUR GANG, AND YOU SUCKERS LET
US JOIN IN A HEARTBEAT.
[laughter]
WHAT’S THE MATTER?
YOU READY TO DROP TO YOUR KNEES
AND BEG FOR MERCY?
>> NAH. ACTUALLY, THAT’S QUITE A
LOAD OFF.
>> HUH?
>> SINCE YOU GUYS HAVE FIRED ME
FROM THE YELLOW SCARVES,
I’M JUST A KID WHO HITS ON
CHICKS.
>> AH?
[door grinding shut]
>> I’M JUST YOUR AVERAGE LOSER
WHO COULDN’T EVEN SAVE THE GIRL
HE LOVED.
I REALIZE NOW I WAS AN IDIOT,
THINKING I COULD TURN MY BACK ON
MY PAST AND BECOME A NORMAL HIGH
SCHOOL STUDENT.
THAT’S WHY I’M HERE.
YOU SEE, ALL I AM IS MASAOMI
KIDA.
>> [grunts]
>> THAT’S RIGHT.
THAT’S WHY I’M HERE TONIGHT!
THE PAST, WHICH HAD BEEN DOGGING
ME FOR SO LONG, HAD SUDDENLY
MOVED ON WITHOUT ME.
>> THERE’S JUST NO ESCAPING IT.
FOREVER AND EVER AND EVER AND
EVER.
A PERSON’S PAST AND THEIR
MEMORIES CAN BE A VERY SOLITARY
BURDEN.
>> YOU SEE, IT’S MY TURN NOW TO
START CHASING THE PAST, RIGHT?
>> HUH?
>> THEY SAY YOUR PAST CAN GET
LONELY.
IF THAT’S TRUE, THEN I NEED TO
CATCH UP TO IT.
>> [groans]
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU BABBLING
ABOUT, YOU DUMBASS?
[crowd murmurs approvingly]
>> JUST SO YOU KNOW, I CAME HERE
TONIGHT KNOWING THAT I MAY DIE.
>> [grunts]
>> BUT WHAT I ALSO KNEW WAS THAT
I WAS READY TO KILL.
WELL, TO BE MORE SPECIFIC,
THE GUY THAT I WANNA KILL
WOULD BE YOU.
>> [strained groaning]
>> I’LL SAY IT AGAIN:
THAT’S WHY I CAME HERE.
AND I WON’T LET ANYONE TAKE THAT
AWAY!
>> AH! COME ON, MOVE!
DON’T JUST STAND THERE.
GET THIS IDIOT!
>> [yelling]
>> WHY DID I HESITATE BEFORE?
IT’S SO SIMPLE.
[grunting]
>> WHAT THE--?
COME ON, HE’S JUST ONE GUY!
>> I AM WHO I AM.
THAT’S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
SAKI, I’M NOT SCARED ANYMORE.
I’LL CATCH MY PAST SOON.
AND THEN I’LL LEAVE IT BEHIND.
>> HURRY! WILL YOU DO SOMETHING
ALREADY?
YOU MORONS ARE TOTALLY USELESS.
[grunts]
OH, RIGHT.
[safety clicks]
>> [yells]
>> [groans]
>> [laughs]
HOW’S THAT FEEL?
TEACH YOU TO MESS WITH ME, YOU
PIECE OF SHIT.
>> [groans]
>> ALL RIGHT, YOUR ASS IS MINE
NOW, PUNK.
HUH?
WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT ARE YOU FREAKING DOING,
DUMBASS?
>> YEAH.
SORRY, BUT IT SEEMS LIKE MOTHER
WILL BE SAD IF YOU WENT AND
KILLED THIS GUY.
SO I DECIDED I HAD TO DO
SOMETHING.
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH, LISTEN.
SORRY.
YOU SEE, I SENSE MOTHER IS GOING
TO BE HERE ANY SECOND.
>> [grunts]
HUH?
>> [gasps]
MASAOMI!
>> ANRI...
WHY ARE YOU...?
>> MASAOMI.
>> MIKADO.
>> MIKADO, WHY?
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
[Butterfly by ON/OFF]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> EVEN NOW, I STILL DON’T GET
IT.
I HAD AN EXPERIENCE THAT WOULD
CHANGE MY LIFE, AND ALTHOUGH IT
WAS PRETTY STRANGE, IT WAS NOT
ALL THAT UNUSUAL.
NEXT TIME, SELFLESS DEVOTION.