[Complication
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK’D]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> WHERE IS MASAOMI, ANYWAY?
>> HE LEFT A LITTLE BIT AGO,
SAID HE HAD SOMETHING TO TAKE
CARE OF.
>> ’CAUSE FROM HERE, THINGS WILL
BEGIN TO SMOLDER AND SMOKE ALL
ON THEIR OWN.
>> YOU AND ME ARE OVER WITH,
FINISHED.
>> YOU DID WHAT YOU THOUGHT WAS
BEST, DIDN’T YOU?
>> SO THIS GUY, HE’S LIKE THE
LEADER OF THE DOLLARS, ISN’T HE?
>> AND IF TURNS OUT THE DOLLARS
ARE MIXED UP IN ANY OF THIS,
THEN WE’LL CRUSH THEM, TOO.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> [panting]
[shouting]
>> THAT WAY!
[thunder crashes]
>> CUT HER OFF OVER THERE!
BLOCK THE EXIT.
[thunder booming]
>> WHY?
WHY IS MASAOMI--
>> THE GIRL RUNS, TRYING TO
ESCAPE THE SHADOWS THAT FOLLOW
HER.
ALL SHE WANTED TO KNOW...
WAS THE TRUTH.
>> OVER HERE!
>> WHAT A PAIN IN THE ASS.
WHERE’D SHE GO?
SHE WON’T GET FAR.
>> WHY IS MASAOMI--WHY?
>> SHE DIDN’T FEEL ANYTHING.
THE SHOCK OF WHAT SHE HAD JUST
SEEN WAS OVERWHELMING.
HER WHOLE BODY HAD GONE NUMB.
>> I HEARD THE GOOD NEWS.
YOU’RE ABLE TO LEAVE THE
HOSPITAL EARLY!
>> EVERYONE’S BEEN SO GREAT.
THANK YOU FOR ALL YOU’VE DONE.
[toy clattering]
>> [grunts]
>> HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THE SLASHER INCIDENTS HAD
STOPPED AFTER THAT NIGHT, AND
THE CITY WAS FINALLY REGAINING A
SENSE OF CALM.
A NORMAL LIFE NOW AWAITED ANRI
SONOHARA.
OR AT LEAST, IT SHOULD HAVE.
>> HEY, ANRI!
I MADE IT.
I THOUGHT I WOULDN’T.
THE STUDENT COUNCIL RAN LONGER
THAN I THOUGHT.
>> MIKADO!
>> I HEARD THAT, STARTING
TOMORROW, YOU’LL BE ABLE TO COME
BACK TO SCHOOL.
YOU SURE YOU’RE OKAY?
>> YEAH, I FEEL FINE.
>> LET ME GET YOUR THINGS.
>> NO! I’M FINE.
THANK YOU, THOUGH.
>> JUST LET HIM CARRY ’EM.
THE POOR SUCKER RAN ALL THE WAY
FROM SCHOOL JUST SO HE COULD DO
THAT FOR YA.
SINCE I’VE SEEN HIM THIS
MORNING, GUESS HOW MANY TIMES
I’VE HEARD HIM SAY THIS:
"ANRI’S GETTING OUT OF THE
HOSPITAL TODAY! I WONDER WHEN
SHE’LL BE ABLE TO COME BACK TO
SCHOOL?
SHE’S SO CUTE, SO BOOBYLICIOUS!"
>> I DIDN’T SAY THAT LAST THING!
>> LISTEN, I JUST WANTED TO SAY
THANKS TO YOU BOTH.
FOR VISITING ME WHILE I WAS IN
THE HOSPITAL.
>> SURE, NO PROBLEM.
HEY, BY THE WAY, MASAOMI, WERE
YOU COMING OUT OF THE HOSPITAL
JUST NOW?
>> UH, YEAH, I WAS.
I WAS LOOKING FOR YOU GUYS.
>> HM.
OH, RIGHT, HEY, ANRI, YOU’RE
WELCOME TO USE THE NOTES I TOOK
WHILE YOU WERE ABSENT.
THEY MIGHT BE KIND OF HARD TO
READ, BUT YOU KNOW, IF YOU WANT
TO BORROW THEM OR SOMETHING,
THAT’S NOT A PROBLEM.
I’LL BE MORE THAN HAPPY TO LEND
THEM TO YOU.
WHERE ARE THEY?
LET’S SEE.
I KNOW THAT I PUT THEM
SOMEWHERE...OH, WAIT, I THINK
THEY’RE IN HERE.
>> SOMETHING’S DIFFERENT ABOUT
MASAOMI.
>> THE GIRL FELT SOMETHING WAS
WRONG WITH THE BOY.
SOMETHING HAD CHANGED.
SHE NOTICED IT THE FIRST TIME HE
CAME TO SEE HER IN THE HOSPITAL.
>> OKAY, YOU SHOULD FEEL BETTER
SOON.
>> MASAOMI.
>> ANRI, ARE YOU...
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I’M FINE. IT’S NOTHING,
REALLY.
I JUST HAD A LITTLE
RUN-IN WITH THE SLASHER.
BUT IT LOOKS WORSE THAN IT IS.
IT’S REALLY NO BIG DEAL.
[phone chiming]
>> SORRY, I GOTTA BOUNCE, GUYS.
I’LL LEAVE IT UP TO YOU, PRINCE
MIKADO, TO MAKE SURE THE
PRINCESS GETS HOME SAFELY.
DON’T BLOW THIS CHANCE WHILE YOU
GOT IT, BUDDY.
SEE YA.
>> YEAH, SEE YA TOMORROW.
>> A HORRIBLE SENSE OF DREAD
BEGAN TO WELL INSIDE HER.
>> LISTEN, TELL THEM NOT TO DO
ANYTHING TILL I GET THERE, OKAY?
[keys clacking]
>> I’VE BEEN SEEING A LOT MORE
YELLOW SCARVES HANGING AROUND
LATELY.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
WITH ALL THAT YELLOW, THOSE GUYS
ARE WAY EASIER TO SPOT THAN THE
DOLLARS ARE.
>> YEAH, THEY’VE BEEN AROUND FOR
A WHILE.
BUT LATELY THEY SEEM KINDA
DIFFERENT.
>> WHAT DO YA MEAN?
>> I DON’T REALLY KNOW FOR SURE.
SOMETHING ABOUT THEM’S CLEARLY
CHANGED, THOUGH.
I GUESS...
THEY JUST SEEM MORE VIOLENT THAN
THEY EVER DID BEFORE.
[chiming tone]
>> OH, HEY, SAIKA, HOW ARE YA?
>> GREETINGS!
>> WELCOME.
>> HI, EVERYONE.
UM...I’M SORRY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU SORRY FOR?
>> YOU WERE KINDA NEW TO THE NET
AND YOU CAUGHT A VIRUS.
THAT TOTALLY EXPLAINS WHY YOU
WERE ACTING THAT WAY, RIGHT?
YOU JUST COULDN’T HELP IT.
>> I’M SORRY, I’M SO SORRY.
>> [chuckles]
YOU APOLOGIZE TOO MUCH.
>> BY THE WAY, SAIKA, HAVE YOU
EVER HEARD OF A GANG CALLED THE
YELLOW SCARVES?
>> YOU MEAN THOSE GUYS I SEE
WEARING YELLOW BANDANAS?
>> THAT’S THEM EXACTLY.
THERE’S ANOTHER GROUP OUT THERE
THAT’S KINDA SIMILAR TO THEM
CALLED THE DOLLARS.
AND NOW BECAUSE OF THAT WHOLE
SLASHER THING THAT WAS
TERRIFYING EVERYONE,
THOSE TWO GANGS ARE FEELING SOME
SERIOUS TENSIONS.
>> UM...
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> LET’S CHANGE THE SUBJECT,
KANRA.
THAT MAYBE ISN’T THE BEST TOPIC
FOR SOMEONE WHO’S A NEWBIE.
>> I DISAGREE.
IF YOU LIVE IN IKEBUKURO, YOU
SHOULD KNOW THIS.
I MEAN, THINK ABOUT IT. THE
SLASHER’S STILL OUT THERE.
THEY NEVER CAUGHT HIM, RIGHT?
BOTH THE DOLLARS AND THE YELLOW
SCARVES HAVE PEOPLE IN THEIR
GANG WHO GOT HIT.
AND EACH SIDE IS ABSOLUTELY
CONVINCED THAT THE OTHER GROUP
IS BEHIND IT ALL.
>> [gasps]
>> I DON’T THINK THE DOLLARS ARE
MAKING THAT BIG OF A DEAL ABOUT
IT.
NEITHER SIDE REALLY KNOWS EACH
OTHER, SO THAT’S CREATING
CONFUSION.
>> DOESN’T MATTER.
IF THE TWO OF THEM DON’T TAKE
MATTERS INTO THEIR OWN HANDS AND
FIND OUT WHO THE SLASHER REALLY
IS, THEN ALL HELL’S GONNA BREAK
LOOSE IN IKEBUKURO.
>> SCARY STUFF.
THIS COULD BE A REAL GANG WAR.
>> DON’T WORRY, ANRI, IT’S OKAY.
IT’S NOT YOUR FAULT THOSE GANGS
ARE OUT OF CONTROL.
YOU WEREN’T THE ONE WHO DID ALL
THOSE ATTACKS.
THERE’S NO REASON TO TURN
YOURSELF IN.
DON’T DO ANYTHING RASH.
THE COPS HAVE BEEN PRETTY SCARY
LATELY.
I MEAN, REALLY SCARY.
THEY’RE JUST PLAIN FRIGHTENING!
LIKE THOSE BIKE COPS.
>> OH, OKAY, THANKS FOR THE TIP.
>> HUH?
OH, RIGHT.
NEXT TIME, I’LL TEACH YOU HOW TO
USE THE PRIVATE MESSAGE MODE.
>> SORRY, BUT I REALLY HAVE TO
GET GOING NOW.
>> OH, OKAY.
GOODNIGHT, SAIKA, TAKE IT EASY.
>> NIGHT.
>> BYE.
WELL, I HAVE TO GET GOING, TOO.
>> GOODNIGHT.
>> SEE YA LATER.
>> HEY, KANRA, ABOUT THE
SLASHER--
>> I’LL LET YOU KNOW IF I HEAR
ANYTHING.
AND I’LL CUT YOU A GOOD RATE.
IF THE SLASHER IS CAUGHT, THEN
MAYBE TENSIONS WILL EASE BETWEEN
THE DOLLARS AND THE YELLOW
SCARVES.
>> [groans]
>> I DON’T KNOW IF IT’LL BE THAT
EASY.
NEITHER THE DOLLARS NOR THE
YELLOW SCARVES BEHAVE LIKE TRULY
COHESIVE GROUPS.
I BET SOME OF THEM WILL USE THE
CURRENT TENSIONS AS AN EXCUSE TO
JUMP THE OTHER GANG WHENEVER
THEY WANT.
>> [chuckling]
>> [panting]
[sirens]
>> IF IT GETS TO THAT POINT,
THEN A REAL GANG WAR IS
INEVITABLE.
>> THEN I WON’T LET IT GET TO
THAT POINT.
>> REALLY?
YOU MAY BE PAST THE POINT OF NO
RETURN ALREADY.
AND IF NOT, YOU HAVE NO CONTROL
OVER THE YELLOW SCARVES.
>> IT DOESN’T MATTER.
I’LL STOP IT.
>> WELL, I HOPE YOU DO.
>> "I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING,"
THOUGHT THE GIRL WITH THE
DEMONIC BLADE UNDER HER SKIN.
"I HAVE TO ACT," THOUGHT THE
GIRL WHO’D WATCHED THE WORLD
PASS BEFORE HER LIKE A MOVIE.
BUT...
THE BOY WHO’D PASSED THROUGH HER
MOVIE AND HAD NOW LANDED A
REGULAR ROLE, HE WAS TRAPPED--
BOUND BY THE HEAVY CHAINS OF HIS
OWN PAST.
[phone chirps]
>> [sighs]
[ringing again]
>> ESCAPE WAS NO LONGER AN
OPTION.
[phone ringing]
>> WHAT’S UP?
GOTCHA.
OKAY, I’LL BE RIGHT THERE.
HANG TIGHT.
SORRY, HAVE TO SPLIT.
I GOT A FRIEND IN NEED.
>> WHAT? YOU’RE LEAVING?
>> HEY, IF YOU NEED TO BLAME
SOMEONE, BLAME MY FRIEND ALL YOU
WANT.
BLAMING A PERSON IS FREE AND IT
CAUSES ME NO HARM.
IT’S JUST LIKE TWO WIVES FOR ONE
DUDE.
LONG LIVE POLYGAMY!
>> POLYGA-WHAT?
>> LATES, PEEPS.
SEE YA TOMORROW!
>> [sighs]
I WONDER WHAT’S SO IMPORTANT.
>> DON’T YOU THINK MASAOMI’S
BEEN ACTING KIND OF WEIRD
LATELY?
>> REALLY?
MAYBE YOU’RE OVERTHINKING IT.
MM, UH...HM.
>> UM, I’M SORRY.
I HAVE TO GO DO SOMETHING TODAY.
BYE.
>> HUH?
>> HEY, I HEARD SOME GUYS FORM
THE DOLLARS GOT JUMPED BY THE
YELLOW SCARVES LAST NIGHT.
>> OH.
>> YEAH, I HEARD IT WAS AN
AMBUSH.
ONE OF ’EM ALMOST GOT KILLED.
>> THE YELLOW SCARVES ARE SAYING
THAT THE DOLLARS ARE THE ONES
BEHIND THE SLASHER ATTACKS.
>> SOMETHING HAD TO BE DONE.
THE BOY WHO LED THE DOLLARS KNEW
THIS.
BUT HE STILL HAD NO IDEA THAT HE
WAS JUST ANOTHER PAWN ON THE
CHESS BOARD.
>> TO ALL GOOD CUSTOMERS, COME,
EAT SUSHI.
SUSHI IS THE SOUL OF JAPAN.
SOUL MUSIC!
>> I WONDER IF IT’S TRUE THAT
SIMON DOES A COSSACK DANCE WHEN
HE DELIVERS SOMEONE’S SUSHI.
>> THOSE KIDS WERE LUCKY.
IF SIMON HADN’T BEEN OUT ON
DELIVERY LAST NIGHT...
>> SWING THAT PIPE AND YOU’LL BE
THE MAIN INGREDIENT AT SUSHI
BAR.
HUMAN SUSHI.
IT NO FEEL GOOD NOR TASTE GOOD
EITHER.
>> LUCK--SOMETHING THAT ALWAYS
RUNS OUT IN THE END.
MAN, THINGS ARE NOT LOOKING
GOOD.
>> DOES ANYONE HAVE INFORMATION
ON THE DOLLARS OR THE YELLOW
SCARVES?
ANYONE?
>> OUR BOSS IS MASAOMI KIDA.
I’VE SEEN THE TWO OF YOU
TOGETHER BEFORE, MOTHER.
>> HE SAID THAT HE WAS OUT TO
GET REVENGE FOR YOU, HIS GOOD
FRIEND.
>> OH, NO.
>> IT WAS HARD FOR HER TO
BELIEVE.
BUT SHE KNEW THE CHILDREN COULD
NOT LIE TO HER.
SHE WAS THEIR MOTHER.
>> WHERE IS HE NOW?
>> HE SHOULD BE AT THE MEETING
TODAY.
>> FINE. PLEASE TAKE ME TO WHERE
THAT IS.
[thunder booming]
>> AND THEN...
SHE FINALLY KNEW EVERYTHING.
>> MASAOMI...
>> HEY, THINK SHE’S BACK HERE?
>> SHE HAD TO RUN.
>> IT’S QUITE SIMPLE.
>> WHY IS MASAOMI--
[voices echoing]
>> ALL OF THEM.
>> CUT THEM UP AND LOVE THEM.
>> I’LL LOVE THEM FOR YOU.
MASAOMI KIDA.
>> WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF SHE GOT
CAUGHT?
>> BECAUSE YOU CAN’T LOVE
OTHERS.
I LOVE THEM.
>> I’LL LOVE THEM FOR YOU.
MASAOMI KIDA.
>> CUT THEM UP AND LOVE THEM.
>> I DON’T WANT TO HURT ANYONE.
>> THE BOY WOULD FIND OUT THAT
SHE’S A MONSTER.
AND THAT THOUGHT MADE HER
TREMBLE WITH FEAR.
>> [grunts]
I CAN’T FIT BACK THERE.
>> I’LL GO.
>> MASAOMI!
SAVE ME, SOMEONE, SAVE ME.
[horse whinnies]
>> HEY!
>> THERE SHE WAS IN THE POURING
RAIN,
THE FEMALE DULLAHAN.
[phone chiming]
>> CORNERED AND TRAPPED, SHE HAD
ONLY ONE CHOICE--
TO SEEK HELP FROM SOMEONE JUST
LIKE HER, SOMEONE ELSE WHO
DIDN’T BELONG IN THIS WORLD.
>> THAT THING JUST USED ITS
FREAKING BIKE TO SCALE THE WALL!
>> YEAH, I BELIEVE THAT.
[phone rings]
>> GET READY.
>> HOLY CRAP.
>> CELTY!
>> YOU CAN FILL ME IN LATER.
JUST GET ON THE BACK.
WE GOTTA GO.
>> OKAY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> HOLD ON TIGHT, OKAY?
[ghostly whinny]
[shouting]
>> YOU KNOW, I’VE SEEN YOU
AROUND TOWN FOR SOME TIME NOW.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THERE WERE WAY
TOO MANY CURVES IN THAT RIDING
OUTFIT YOU WEAR FOR YOU TO
ACTUALLY BE A GUY.
NOW GUYS DON’T REALLY DO IT
FOR ME,
BUT IF YOU ARE A GIRL, I COULD
EASILY FALL IN LOVE WITH THAT
SUIT.
IT’S HOT.
A CHICK’S ONLY AS FINE AS HER
CLOTHES.
>> HUH? THIS IS THE GUY WHO’S
ALWAYS AROUND MIKADO AND ANRI.
>> HM?
>> OH, I SEE.
SHE DOESN’T WANT HIM TO SEE HER
FACE.
I DON’T KNOW WHAT’S GOING ON,
BUT I GET IT.
[gasping]
[ghostly neighing]
[shouting]
>> GAH! DAMN IT.
NOW YOU’RE DEAD!
>> NO, DON’T!
>> SHE LOOKED JUST LIKE THE
HEADLESS KNIGHT OF THE LEGENDS.
[hoofbeats]
>> THE SCRAPS OF INFORMATION
THEY HAD ALL STARTED COMING
TOGETHER.
THE INTRUDER CARRIED A SWORD
MUCH LIKE THE SLASHER’S.
THE BLACK BIKE, LONG RUMORED TO
BE PART OF THE DOLLARS, SUDDENLY
CAME TO HER RESCUE.
THEY ALL REACHED THE SAME
CONCLUSION.
THE SLASHER WAS PART OF THE
DOLLARS.
THE BOY WASN’T ABSOLUTELY SURE
IF HIS CONCLUSION WAS RIGHT.
BUT HE REALIZED THAT DIDN’T
MATTER.
BECAUSE REGARDLESS OF WHAT HE
THOUGHT, HE NOW KNEW HE’D NO
LONGER BE ABLE TO HOLD HIS
COMPANIONS AT BAY.
>> HEY, EVER HEARD OF THE
DULLAHAN?
>> WHA--?
NO. WHAT?
>> ACCORDING TO THE LEGENDS,
IT’S A HEADLESS KNIGHT.
AND IT RIDES AROUND ON A
HEADLESS HORSE, VISITING THOSE
ABOUT TO DIE.
IT’S BASICALLY JUST LIKE THE
GRIM REAPER.
>> SUDDENLY, IT CAME TO HIM.
SOME OF THEM MIGHT DIE.
WHY IS THAT?
WHY DO TIMES LIKE THIS MAKE ME
WANT TO SEE SAKI?
>> "THE BLUE SKY IS DEAD,
MEANING EVERYTHING IS FALLING"
READ THE BANNER WHEN THE ARMY OF
THE YELLOW SCARVES ROSE IN THE
STORY OF THE THREE KINGDOMS.
>> THE SKY AIN’T BLUE YET.
THEN AGAIN, IT ISN’T YELLOW
EITHER.
>> GOOD EVENING.
OH, JUST YOU, TARO?
>> HEY, THERE.
YEAH, I GUESS.
>> STRAIGHT TO PRIVATE MESSAGE,
HUH?
>> THERE’S SOMETHING I NEED TO
ASK YOU.
UM, HAVE THE YELLOW SCARVES BEEN
IN IKEBUKURO FOR A WHILE NOW?
>> WELL, FOR ABOUT THREE YEARS
OR SO.
AT FIRST, THEY WERE A QUIET
LITTLE GROUP.
>> THE BOY WHO LED THE DOLLARS
LEARNED OF THE HORRIBLE FIGHT
BETWEEN THE YELLOW SCARVES AND
THE BLUE SQUARES,
NEVER KNOWING THE GIRL
SACRIFICED WAS THE FORMER
GIRLFRIEND OF HIS BEST FRIEND.
AND UNAWARE THAT THE PERSON
TELLING HIM THIS WAS THE SAME
MAN WHO CONTROLLED THAT GIRL’S
MIND, AND HAD PERMANENTLY
SCARRED HIS BEST FRIEND.
>> SO THE ONLY ONES LEFT WERE
THE YELLOW SCARVES.
>> NOT REALLY.
THE BLUE SQUARES DIDN’T ACTUALLY
GO AWAY.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> THE LEADER OF THE YELLOW
SCARVES GOT SICK OF FIGHTING AND
LEFT.
AND THEN AFTER HE WAS GONE,
MOST OF THE BLUE SQUARES JOINED
THE YELLOW SCARVES.
>> SO BASICALLY THEY JUST
MERGED?
>> YEAH, BASICALLY.
WITH THE LEADER GONE, NO ONE WAS
REALLY CHECKING WHERE PEOPLE
CAME FROM ANYMORE.
SO NOBODY KNEW IF YOU WERE
PREVIOUSLY PART OF THE OTHER
GROUP.
ALL SOMEONE HAD TO DO WAS REMOVE
THEIR BLUE AND SAY THAT THEY
WANTED TO JOIN.
THAT WAS IT.
>> AND SO THE GUY WHO QUIT,
THE LEADER...
>> I WOULD IMAGINE HE HAS NO
IDEA THAT THE GUYS RESPONSIBLE
FOR SENDING HIS OLD GIRLFRIEND
TO THE HOSPITAL ARE NOW IN HIS
OWN GANG.
>> [gasps]
>> YOU SHOULD BE CAREFUL, TOO.
IT SEEMS THE DOLLARS HAVE A FEW
YELLOW SCARVES AMONGST THEM AS
WELL.
>> YEAH, BUT THAT MIGHT WORK IN
MY FAVOR.
IF I SPREAD WORD THAT THE
DOLLARS HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH
THE SLASHER, THEN THAT MIGHT GET
PASSED ON TO THE YELLOW SCARVES.
>> PROVIDING THE DOLLARS REALLY
WEREN’T INVOLVED.
THE DOLLARS DON’T HAVE ANY
RULES, AND YOU DON’T KEEP ANY
EYE ON EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM.
I MEAN, THINK ABOUT IT...
SOME GUYS IN THE DOLLARS COULD
BE WORKING WITH THE SLASHER
WITHOUT YOU KNOWING.
AFTER ALL, THAT’S HOW THE
DOLLARS WORK.
IF YOU’RE GOING TO GET YOURSELF
INVOLVED IN THIS WORLD,
YOU NEED TO BE PREPARED AND LOOK
AT THE WHOLE PICTURE.
>> I’LL KEEP THAT IN MIND.
>> MORNING.
MORNING!
>> OH, HEY, GOOD MORNING.
>> WHAT’S THE MATTER?
YOU SEEM LIKE YOU’RE A LITTLE
DOWN TODAY.
YOU SURE YOU’RE READY TO COME
BACK TO SCHOOL?
>> I’M FINE, REALLY.
>> MORNIN’.
>> MORNING.
>> OH, HEY, I RAN INTO MASAOMI
AT THE TRAIN STATION.
SAID HE WASN’T COMIN’ TODAY.
>> HUH?
HOW COME?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA. HE DIDN’T
REALLY GIVE ME A REASON WHY.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> LATER.
>> YEAH, THANKS, MAN.
>> YOU CAN’T KEEP RUNNING FROM
YOUR PAST, MASAOMI.
I MEAN, THAT’S WHAT THIS IS
ABOUT. SOMETHING FROM YOUR PAST
HAS YOU WORRIED, RIGHT?
SO STOP RUNNING.
TURN AROUND, FIGHT THIS THING,
AND WIN.
>> I WISH IT WERE THAT SIMPLE.
IF I COULD SETTLE OUR PAST JUST
BY FIGHTING, THEN I’D GLADLY DO
IT.
>> WELL, WHY CAN’T YOU DO THAT?
>> ’CAUSE I CAN’T FIGHT YOU,
SAKI.
IT’S NOT POSSIBLE.
>> HE JUST WANTED A PLACE WHERE
HE BELONGED.
EVERY TIME HE TALKED WITH HIS
CHILDHOOD FRIEND ABOUT THIS NEW
CITY HE LIVED IN, HE REALIZED
THAT HE WAS ACTUALLY JUST A
STRANGER IN HIS OWN SKIN.
THEN IT CAME TO HIM.
THE ONLY PERSON AND PLACE THAT
HE EVER TRULY FELT AT HOME WAS
WHEN HE WAS WITH ONE GIRL,
SAKI MIKAJIMA.
AND NOW HIS MOTIVATIONS WERE
DRIVEN BY HIS DEAR FRIEND, THE
HEART OF HIS NEW LIFE.
>> MAN, IT’S STARTIN’ TO RAIN
AGAIN.
>> KYOHEI.
>> both: HUH?
>> YOU CAME BACK.
>> I DID.
LET’S TALK SOMEWHERE ELSE.
[Butterfly by ON/OFF]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> A GREAT MAN ONCE SAID,
"REALITY IS AN ILLUSION."
>> A GREAT MAN ONCE SAID, "THE
WORLD IS SYMBOLIC."
>> A HORRIBLE PAST IS THE
PRODUCT OF DELUSION.
>> THAT REALITY NEVER EXISTED.
WE CAN JUST LEAVE IT BE.
>> NEXT TIME, A NEW KING WILL
ARISE.