[Uragiri no Yuyake
by Theater Brook]
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> THE DOLLARS?
>> THAT’S THE ANGEL WHO FLIES
THROUGH THE SKY, FLASHING HER
PANTIES, SINGING, "PIPIRU, PIRU,
PIRU."
>> AND, YO, DON’T USE TOO MUCH.
IF SHE DON’T WAKE UP, THEY’RE
GONNA TAKE IT OUT OF OUR PAY.
>> THEY’RE KIND OF A MYSTERY.
WE DON’T KNOW A WHOLE LOT ABOUT
THEM EITHER.
BUT SINCE YOU’RE HERE, I’LL TELL
YOU WHAT WE DO KNOW.
>> THEY’RE SORT OF LIKE A COLOR
GANG, BUT NO ONE KNOWS WHAT
COLOR THEY ARE.
WHAT’S THE POINT, RIGHT?
>> THE NEW DENGEKI BUNKO SERIES
HIT TODAY.
>> WE EACH GET 10 COPIES FOR
OTHER REASONS.
>> YEAH, OTHER REASONS.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> [laughs]
THINK THAT YOU CAN JUST SLIP
AWAY?
WRONG! AND TURNING RIGHT!
[screaming]
>> A REAL MAN USES HIS ABS.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
WE’VE DONE SOMETHING LIKE THIS
SINCE WE JOINED THE DOLLARS.
RIGHT, KYOHEI?
>> HEY, SIT YOUR ASS BACK DOWN.
>> ABOUT THE DOLLARS. AND
YOU’RE NOT AN ANGEL THAT FLIES
THROUGH THE SKY, SHOUTING
"PI-PIRU, PIRU, PIRU," FLASHING
HER PANTIES. RIGHT, DOTACHIN?
>> I TOLD YOU, DON’T CALL ME
THAT!
>> HA. WE LOST ’EM.
>> [laughs]
AH!
OH!
THEY’RE INSANE!
>> [grunts]
>> [pants]
[grunts]
UGH!
>> I THINK IT’S TIME WE HAD A
LITTLE CHAT ABOUT THOSE HUMAN
EXPERIMENTS YOU PRICKS ARE
INVOLVED WITH.
THE NAME’S KYOHEI KADOTA.
AND IF THERE’S ONE THING I
REALLY HATE, IT’S BEING CALLED
DOTACHIN.
NOW LET’S BACK THIS UP TO
WHERE IT BEGAN EIGHT HOURS AGO.
THE STORY YOU’RE ABOUT TO HEAR
IS NOW KNOWN AS THE LEGENDARY
KAZUTANO INCIDENT.
>> THE GIRL WHO WENT MISSING WAS
A CLASSMATE OF MINE.
WELL, A FRIEND OF A FRIEND, TO
BE EXACT.
TO BE HONEST, I’VE NEVER
ACTUALLY MET HER AT ALL.
>> WHAT? YOU’RE SAYING YOU HAD
A FRIEND GO MISSING?
>> I SEEMS A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE
BEEN DISAPPEARING LATELY.
RUMORS ABOUT THESE CASES ARE
EVERYWHERE RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU DO LIKE RUMORS, KANRA.
>> [laughs]
ALL THE RUMORS I’VE HEARD ARE
ABOUT ILLEGAL FOREIGNERS, OR
MAYBE A RUNAWAY, NEW TO THE BIG
CITY.
BASICALLY, THEY ARE PEOPLE THAT
NOBODY CAN TRACE WHEN THEY
DISAPPEAR.
FOR SOME REASON, MOST OF THESE
INCIDENTS HAVE OCCURRED BETWEEN
IKEBUKURO AND SHIBUYA.
AND ONCE THEY’RE GONE,
THAT’S IT.
THEY’RE GONE FOR GOOD.
>> YOU SERIOUS?
>> OH, BUT THERE’S ANOTHER RUMOR
THAT’S EVEN SCARIER.
GET THIS.
THEY SAY THE REASON THEY’RE
NEVER FOUND IS ’CAUSE THEY’RE
TAKEN BY THE DOLLARS.
WHEN THEY’RE DONE WITH THEM,
THEY EAT THEM!
>> WHAT?
>> HMM?
>> DIGGIN’ THE RUSTY SIGN.
>> THIS IS IT.
THIS MUST BE THE PLACE
THE INTEL BROKER MENTIONED.
>> HAS TO BE.
LOOKS LIKE A GOOD PLACE TO
FIND ILLEGALS TO ME.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET’S GET BUSY AND
START EARNIN’ SOME OF THAT CASH.
>> [grunts]
all: HUH?
>> THEY’RE HERE!
[screaming and excitement]
>> [laughs]
>> [whimpers]
[screaming]
>> KAZUTANO!
[whimpers]
[cries]
>> [hums to music]
>> SHUT UP! YOU SCARED?
HUH? YOU SCARED NOW?
YOU EVEN MORE SCARED?
>> [screams]
>> NICE! TEENAGE GIRLS.
20% EXTRA.
>> NAH, STICK WITH THE USUAL.
I DON’T WANT TO GO GETTIN’
GREEDY AND HAVE YOU-KNOW-WHO
SHOW UP.
>> YOU MEAN, THE HEADLESS--
>> I SAY WE JUST BAG THIS GUY
TODAY.
>> HMM? WHAT’S UP?
>> [sings to music]
>> YOU DON’T THINK HE’S A FEW
FRIES SHORT OF A HAPPY MEAL?
>> WHO CARES, IT’S A HUMAN.
>> FINE. BUT HE’S CLEARLY GOT
SOME WEAR AND TEAR.
THEY WON’T PAY FULL PRICE
FOR HIM.
>> [hums]
>> YO!
>> EH?
>> WELL, HEY THERE, MEAL TICKET.
all: [laugh]
>> YOU SEE ME, I JAPANESE!
I LOOK-A JUST-A LIKE YOU, RIGHT?
BUT PEOPLE SAY I LOOK-A FOREIGN.
I SO SAD.
WHY-A YOU THINK-A THEY PICK ON
ME?
[classical music in headphones]
[chase music]
>> [struggles]
>> WE’RE NOT GETTIN’ RICH OFF
THIS ONE.
>> AND WHAT THE HELL DOES "I SO"
MEAN?
>> SO IF YOU REALLY THINK ABOUT
IT, WITHOUT A LITTLE-BROTHER
HELPER-FAIRY CHARACTER LIKE
YUUTA, HE’S REALLY JUST
A MASOCHISTIC WOLF WITH A HAIR
FETISH.
>> NO, NO, NO. HE’S MORE LIKE A
CROSS-DRESSING BOY THAN A LITTLE
BROTHER TYPE.
I’D PREFER A LITTLE SISTER
HELPER FAIRY.
OR OLDER SISTER, EITHER WAY.
>> CAN YOU GUYS NOT TALK ABOUT
THAT SHIT WHEN WE’RE EATING?
>> DOTACHIN, LET’S GRAB SOME
FOOD!
HUNGRY, HUNGRY!
>> HEY.
>> WOW, CHECK IT OUT. YOU DO
THIS ALL YOURSELF, KYOHEI? IT’S
AWESOME.
>> THIS JOHN’S BIGGER THAN MY
APARTMENT.
>> YEAH, IT’S HUGE. THEY SAID
THE CONCEPT IS A HIGH-CLASS
FLOOR SHOW IN A LAID-BACK
ENVIRONMENT.
>> HUH.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET’S GET GOING.
THIS DAY ONLY COMES ONCE
A MONTH.
WE DON’T WANT TO MISS IT.
>> RIGHT.
[cell phone beeps]
>> WHO’S THAT?
>> IT’S KAZUTANO. HE SAYS,
"I BROKE A PLATE."
>> SO WHAT? GET A NEW ONE.
>> TIME FOR THE DOLLAR STORE!
>> [screams]
I AM JAPANESE! YOU MAKE-A
MISTAKE! [whimpers]
>> HERE.
>> MAYBE HE SCREWED UP HIS KANJI
AND REALLY MEANT TO SAY THAT
HE’D BEEN KIDNAPPED.
>> [laughs] THERE’S NO WAY.
>> [screams]
>> COME ON! MAKE HIM SHUT UP
ALREADY!
>> ON IT.
>> [struggles]
[grunts] OH!
>> OH!
>> [grunts]
>> IT’S GOOD. IT’S FRESH.
AND NUMBER ONE, IT CHEAP.
>> SO THEN, YOU HEARD THAT
RUMOR, TOO, HUH, ANRI?
>> I DID.
>> DON’T WORRY ABOUT IT.
THAT WHOLE THING’S A BUNCH
OF B.S.
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
JUST BECAUSE MIKA HAS GONE
MISSING, IT DOESN’T MEAN SHE
WAS ACTUALLY KIDNAPPED.
>> I MEAN, I REALLY DOUBT SOME
GANG GRABBED HER, KILLED HER,
AND THEN TRIED TO--UH--
>> EVER HEARD OF SOMETHING
CALLED TACT?
>> I SCREWED UP.
>> HERE WE ARE.
NIGIRI SUSHI FOR THREE.
IT OKAY, IT FISH SUSHI.
OUR SUSHI NOT MADE FROM HUMAN,
EVEN ON HALF-PRICE DAY.
all: HUH?
>> GO ON--
>> NOW HE’S TALKING ABOUT THIS?
SIMON, I THINK YOUR BANNER
OUTSIDE FELL DOWN.
>> MY BANNER?
>> YEAH, I SAW IT, TOO.
UH, LET’S GO FIX IT. I’LL HELP.
[overlapping chatter]
>> HEY, SABURO, WANT TO
ITASHA-OUT YOUR RIDE?
COME ON, IT’LL BE SO COOL.
>> WANT TO DIE?
>> ITALIAN CARS ARE TOO
EXPENSIVE.
BUY LOCAL.
>> ONE MORE MANTIS SHRIMP HERE,
PLEASE.
>> YELLOW TAIL AND HORSE
MACKEREL, PLEASE.
>> OH!
WHAT A DICK.
>> WITHOUT A DOUBT.
>> WHAT KIND OF A FREAKIN’
JACKASS SPILLS A WHOLE BOTTLE ON
HIMSELF?
>> IT’S NO GOOD. I CAN’T...
KEEP GOING.
>> STAY AWAKE, ’TIL WE DROP OFF
THE GOODS.
>> HUH?
>> OH, THIS BLOWS! MY EYELIDS
WON’T STAY OPEN.
>> WATCH THE ROAD! [groans]
>> UH, EXCUSE-A ME.
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH, WELL, HE WHY YOU
SLEEPY, THROW HIM AWAY LIKE
TRASH, AND YOU GET BETTER.
>> HUH?
>> [snores]
>> KAZUTANO! WE BROUGHT YOU
SOME SUSHI!
>> YO! AND WE BROUGHT YOU
A PLATE FROM THE RUSSIA SUSHI
PLACE.
>> WHA--WHAT THE HELL?
>> SO I’M GUESSING "I BROKE
A PLATE" ISN’T WHAT HE REALLY
MEANT TO TELL US.
>> NO.
>> HE MEANT A BOWL.
>> [grunts]
>> DOTACHIN
>> SIMPLE KANJI CONVERTER.
>> WHAT HAS HE DONE NOW?
[plate breaks]
all: HUH?
>> HE HAD TO HAVE BEEN TAKEN BY
THE LOWLIFES WHO TRAFFIC HUMANS.
HE’S GONE FOR GOOD NOW.
HOW THE HELL AM I GONNA GET BY
WITHOUT KAZUTANO AROUND?
HE’S THE ONLY THING IN MY LIFE
THAT WAS EVER ANY GOOD!
>> WE ALL LIKE KAZUTANO.
BUT FOR SABURO, THE IDEA OF
LOSING HIM WAS ESPECIALLY HARD.
NO ONE CAN FILL HIS SHOES.
IT KIND OF BUMS ME OUT THAT
NOT EVEN ERIKA, WALKER, OR
MYSELF CAN BE THERE FOR SABURO
LIKE THAT.
>> IF HE WAS KIDNAPPED RIGHT
WHEN THAT EMAIL CAME, THEN IT
WASN’T THAT LONG AGO.
WE’RE GONNA FIND HIM BEFORE THEY
DROP HIM OFF, I PROMISE YOU.
AND THEN WE’LL BRING HIM BACK.
>> BUT HOW ARE WE GONNA DO THAT?
>> [grunts]
>> I KNOW.
all: HUH?
>> I HID. BUT I SAW THE CAR THEY
DRIVE.
>> HASIM!
>> YOU’RE IT!
>> YOU’RE THE PERFECT LITTLE
BROTHER-TYPE HELPER-FAIRY
CHARACTER!
>> IT HAS BEEN RUMORED
THAT ON THE OUTSKIRTS OF...
>> YEAH? YEAH, I GOT IT.
IF AND WHEN SHE FINDS THESE
GUYS, MAKE SURE SHE GETS THE
FOREIGNER AND KEEPS HIM OUT OF
HARM’S WAY.
>> EXACTLY. WE HAVE NO IDEA WHEN
THEY’RE SUPPOSED TO HOOK UP WITH
THEIR BUYER AND DROP HIM OFF.
SO WE’RE TRYING TO GET TO HIM AS
SOON AS POSSIBLE.
>> OKAY, IT’S A BLACK VAN,
RIGHT?
DO YOU HAVE THE LICENSE PLATE
NUMBER?
>> YEAH, YOU READY?
>> NO, UH, GIVE ME A SEC.
>> OKAY.
>> UH.
>> THANKS FOR EVERYTHING, HASIM.
>> SURE. DO YOU LIKE SUSHI?
>> YEAH.
>> SEE YA.
>> THERE WASABI?
>> YEAH, SURE.
>> DON’T WORRY, KID.
RUSSIAN WASABI ISN’T SPICY.
>> DON’T LIE TO THE LITTLE GUY
LIKE THAT.
>> LET’S GO.
>> YEAH.
>> BLACK VAN, OKAY? HERE’S THE
PLATE NUMBER FOR YA.
>> BE CAREFUL.
>> THESE GUYS ARE JUST HIRED
GUNS FOR SOME EVIL CORPORATION.
THEY’RE BASICALLY HENCHMEN.
THEY KIDNAP INDIVIDUALS WHO
WON’T BE TRACKED, LIKE
FOREIGNERS, AND THEN HAND THEM
OVER FOR CASH.
THE PEOPLE THEY TAKE ARE
PROBABLY BEING USED AS SUBJECTS
FOR ALL KINDS OF UGLY THINGS.
>> IT’S NO DIFFERENT THAN
CANNIBALISM.
>> OUR GUYS ON THE STREET
HAVEN’T TURNED MUCH IN THIS
MONTH.
>> WELL, IT SEEMS OUT SUBJECTS
HAVE BECOME A LITTLE BIT
CAUTIOUS OF--
>> I DON’T WANT EXCUSES. IF OUR
GUYS CAN’T PRODUCE MORE, THEY’RE
FIRED.
>> BUT, CHIEF--
>> OR PERHAPS YOU WOULD LIKE TO
BECOME A SUBJECT.
GO NOW.
[door opens, closes]
SEIJI.
>> IDIOT!
>> [singing indistinctly]
[cell phone ringing, vibrating]
>> WE LOOKED EVERYWHERE WE COULD
THINK OF FOR THAT BLACK VAN AND
KAZUTANO.
WE THOUGHT FOR SURE WE WOULD
FIND HIM AND SAVE HIM.
WE PULLED OUT EVERY TRICK WE
HAD, BUT AFTER ALL THAT, WE
STILL CAME UP WITH NOTHING.
A SENSE OF DREAD STARTED TO
CREEP IN.
I BEGAN TO WONDER IF I’D EVER
HEAR HIS CLASSIC LINES AGAIN.
I’VE HEARD HIS TIMELESS PHRASES
SO OFTEN, IT ALWAYS TAKES ME
BACK TO BEING A KID.
I FIGURED WHEN I GREW UP, HIS
WORDS WOULD BECOME A THING OF
THE PAST.
>> WE HAVE GOT THE TICKETS!
YOU NEED-A TICKETS!
>> THAT’S RIGHT.
KAZUTANO WAS THE LAST OF
A DYING BREED.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, IT WAS THIS
GUY HERE WHO GAVE SABURO THE
BIGGEST THRILL OF HIS ENTIRE
LIFE...
[Japanese pop music]
TICKETS TO SEE RURI HIJIRIBE.
SABURO HAS SOME MAD LOVE FOR
THIS GODDESS.
HE’S BY FAR HER BIGGEST FAN.
KAZUTANO SET HIM UP WITH
FRONT-ROW TICKETS TO A SHOW NO
ONE WAS ABLE TO GET TICKETS TO.
♪ ♪
WE’VE GOT TO FIND HIM, IF FOR NO
OTHER REASON THAN OUT OF RESPECT
FOR SABURO.
>> DOTACHIN, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
>> AND JUST WHO TO?
>> WELL, UH--
>> YOU KNOW, I WAS THINKING, WHY
DON’T WE TRY TO CALL HIS CELL
PHONE?
YOU NEVER KNOW.
HE MIGHT STILL HAVE IT ON HIM.
>> YEAH, AND IF WE CAN REACH
HIM, MAYBE WE CAN NEGOTIATE WITH
THE KIDNAPPERS.
>> [gasps]
[line trilling]
>> SUSHI LOVE, ESPECIALLY FATTY
TUNA.
>> WHAT THE HELL?
WHO’S THIS?
>> OH, IT’S YOU, DOTACHIN.
I WAS JUST WALKING AND CAME
ACROSS THIS GUY SLEEPING.
SO, WHEN HIS PHONE RANG,
I ANSWERED.
HMM?
WHERE AM I?
I’M OUT IN FRONT OF TAISHOUKEN
IN SOUTH IKEBUKURO.
[chuckles] WHY?
BECAUSE RUSSIA SUSHI’S GOT
A SPECIAL TODAY.
>> [groans in disgust]
IZAYA!
STAY OUT OF IKEBUKURO!
>> WELL, IT SEEMS SHIZU-CHAN HAS
FOUND ME.
SEE YOU.
>> IZAYA!
>> WAKE UP!
WAKE UP, DAMN IT!
COME ON, WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG
WITH YOU?
WAKE UP ALREADY!
>> HEY, BACK IN THE BAG WITH
THOSE.
YOU’LL PUT HIM TO SLEEP FOR
GOOD.
>> BUT THE LONGER WE WAIT TO
FIND KAZUTANO, THEN--
>> SHE’S RIGHT.
THE LONGER WE WAIT MEANS THE
CLOSER THEY GET TO KILLING HIM.
>> HMM.
>> [moaning softly]
>> [grunts]
>> SO WHAT’S THE PLAN?
>> I’M GONNA HAVE HIS BUDDIES
TELL US EXACTLY WHERE THAT
DROP-OFF PLACE IS.
>> THEY SHOULD BE HERE ANY
MINUTE NOW.
THE HIGHER-UPS WILL BE COMING,
SO LOOK SHARP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> LOOKY! ME A-JAPANESE!
WHY CAN’T YOU SEE THAT YOU ARE
MAKING A MISTAKE A-GIGANTICA?
>> LET IT GO.
>> SO, ON YOUR BIRTH
CERTIFICATE, YOU’RE SAYING IT
SAYS "JAPANESE" ON THERE, HUH?
>> THE RUB IS THERE, YOU SEE?
IT BURN UP DURING FIERY AIR
RAIDS.
>> OH, COME ON, YOU’RE NOT THAT
OLD.
[cell phone rings]
YEAH?
>> HEY, MAN, IT’S ME.
>> OH, KANAZAWA.
YOU FINALLY WAKE UP?
>> YEAH, SORRY.
I’M ON MY WAY NOW.
BUT, UH, I FORGOT WHERE WE’RE
SUPPOSED TO MEET.
>> UH, YOU GOT CRAP FOR BRAINS.
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
[all shouting joyfully]
>> HEY, WHO ARE YOU GUYS?
>> all: WE ARE...
THE DOLLARS!
>> THAT’S RIGHT, AND DON’T YOU
FORGET IT!
>> I’M SO SLEEPY.
>> LET’S GO.
THE REASON ALL OF US JOINED
THE DOLLARS IS PRETTY SIMPLE.
SABURO, WALKER, AND ERIKA JUST
TOOK TO ME, AND BEFORE I KNEW
IT, WE WERE HANGING OUT ALL THE
TIME.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THEY SEE IN
A GUY LIKE ME.
TOGETHER, WE’RE A PRETTY RAGTAG
GROUP.
AND THEN ONE DAY I GOT AN EMAIL
ON MY CELL THAT SAID, "DO YOU
WANT TO JOIN THE DOLLARS?
THERE ARE NO RULES OR
RESTRICTIONS.
JUST SAY YOU’RE IN, AND YOU’RE
PART OF THE DOLLARS."
IT WAS AN ODD INVITE, BUT
EVERYONE SAID THE DOLLARS WERE
WEIRD, AT THE VERY LEAST
DIFFERENT.
I KIND OF THOUGHT THE EMAIL WAS
A JOKE, BUT I AGREED TO JOIN
ANYWAY.
AND THE NEXT DAY, THEY SENT ME A
URL AND A PASSWORD.
WHEN I LOGGED IN, MY USERNAME
WAS DISPLAYED RIGHT THERE ON THE
DOLLARS’ WEBSITE.
NO ONE, INCLUDING ME, HAS EVER
SEEN OR MET THE LEADER.
WE DON’T EVEN KNOW WHO IT IS.
THERE ARE SEVERAL SMALLER CELLS
WITHIN THE LARGER GROUP, EACH
BEING PART OF A VERTICAL
HIERARCHY, BUT NO ONE HAS ANY
IDEA WHO’S ON TOP.
AND SINCE THERE’S NO ONE AT THE
TOP SHOUTING DOWN ORDERS,
I DON’T FEEL LIKE I’M WORKING
FOR ANYONE, BUT I’D BE LYING IF
I TOLD YOU I WASN’T AT ALL
CURIOUS AS TO WHO’S BEHIND THIS
ORGANIZATION.
JUST BETWEEN YOU AND ME, I’VE
GOT MY SUSPICIONS ON WHO THAT
GUY MAY BE.
I BET YOU ANYTHING IT’S THAT
ASSHOLE WHO STARTED CALLING ME
DOTACHIN.
>> MMM, FATTY TUNA IS THE BEST.
HMM?
GETTING COLDER.
YOU WON’T FIND WHAT YOU’RE
LOOKING FOR THERE.
>> OH!
OH, CRAP, CELTY.
I’M SORRY.
>> SO, THEN, HOW MUCH DO YOU
THINK THEY’LL GIVE US FOR HIM?
>> WELL, I GUESS WE’RE NOT
GETTING TOO MUCH.
>> YEAH, YOU’RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
[tires squealing]
THINK THAT’S THE BOSS?
>> GOT TO BE.
HUH?
[gasps]
[tires screeching]
WHAT THE HELL?
>> KAZUTANO!
>> KAZUTANO, WE’RE COMING!
HANG TIGHT!
>> PREPARE TO MEET YOUR DOOM.
>> YOU’RE DEAD.
>> WHOA, CLASSIC LINE.
>> WHO SAYS "MEET YOUR DOOM"?
[distant engine whirring]
>> HUH?
[both gasp fearfully]
>> THE HEADLESS RIDER!
>> BUT WE PLAYED IT SAFE AND
TOOK AN OLD GUY!
AAH!
LISTEN, WE WON’T DO IT ANYMORE,
I SWEAR!
>> WHAT THE HELL?
KAZUTANO!
>> DOTACHEENO.
[engine turning]
>> HEY, STOP THEM!
[tires squealing]
>> [laughing]
YOU THINK THAT YOU CAN JUST SLIP
AWAY?
WRONG!
AND TURNING RIGHT!
[tires squealing]
[dog sniffing]
[barks]
>> SHOULD I JUST GO HOME?
>> YO, TIME FOR YOU TO COUGH UP
WHERE IT IS YOU’RE DROPPING OFF
YOUR GOODS.
>> AH, COME ON, IT’S NO FUN AT
ALL IF WE DON’T GET TO TORTURE
THEM A LITTLE FIRST.
HERE, YOU CAN PICK ANY OF THESE
BOOKS YOU WANT.
>> AND THEN WE’LL TORTURE YOU
EXACTLY LIKE THEY DO IN THE
BOOK.
>> WHATEVER.
YOU GUYS CAN HAVE YOUR FUN.
BUT NO GASOLINE IN THE CAR THIS
TIME, OKAY?
>> GASO--
>> SABURAWNO!
TIME FOR THE MORNING RITUAL.
>> OKAY, FINE!
I’LL TALK!
I’LL TELL YOU EVERYTHING!
JUST LET ME OUT OF HERE!
>> YAGIRI PHARMA, HUH?
>> THAT’S A BIG-ASS CORPORATION.
>> YOU GUYS REALLY THINK THAT’S
TRUE?
YOU REALLY THINK THEY EXPERIMENT
ON HUMANS IN THERE?
>> SITTING THERE, LOOKING AT THE
FRONT OF THE BUILDING, IT DID
SEEM PRETTY HARD TO BELIEVE.
BUT THAT SAID, MOST THINGS
GENERALLY DO HAVE TWO SIDES TO
IT, ESPECIALLY IN IKEBUKURO.
THERE’S STUFF HIDDEN AROUND HERE
THAT WOULD BLOW YOUR MIND.
COME ON, WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GO
GET SOMETHING TO EAT?
>> I’M IN.
>> WE GO FOR BREAKFAST AT
RUSSIA SUSHI.
>> YEAH, PERFECT.
LET’S GO.
>> THEN IT’S DECIDED.
>> OF COURSE, DEAR, YOU CAN TAKE
ALL THE MONEY YOU WANT.
IT’S NO PROBLEM.
>> THANKS A LOT, SIS.
>> BYE, SEIJI.
>> LET’S GO.
>> AND THAT’S THE LEGENDARY
KAZUTANO INCIDENT.
FOR US, WE’RE JUST GLAD WE GOT
OUR FRIEND BACK SAFE AND SOUND.
IT’S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> NOISY, ANNOYING, AND PISSING
ME OFF.
WHEN MY ANGER BOILS OVER, MY
BODY STARTS TO ACT ON ITS OWN.
THERE’S NO REGARD FOR MY OWN
WELL-BEING.
NEXT TIME, BAD-ASS DUDE.
BUT I ABSOLUTELY HATE VIOLENCE!