[Uragiri no Yuyake
by Theater Brook]
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> WHOA, CHECK IT OUT.
THAT CHICK IS TOTALLY GETTING
BULLIED.
>> AND TURNING RIGHT!
>> I THINK IT’S TIME THAT WE HAD
A LITTLE CHAT ABOUT THOSE HUMAN
EXPERIMENTS YOU PRICKS ARE
INVOLVED WITH.
>> WAS REAL, AND IT WAS ME.
I KNOW IT.
WHAT WAS I DOING THAT NIGHT?
>> THERE YOU ARE.
I’VE FOUND YOU, MY LOVE.
>> I DON’T WANT EXCUSES.
OR PERHAPS YOU WOULD LIKE TO
BECOME A SUBJECT.
>> LET IT GO.
MAYBE YOU ARE COMPLETE WITHOUT
YOUR HEAD.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> HOW COME WHEN YOU LOSE STUFF,
IT’S ALWAYS THE GOOD STUFF?
>> SAY, LIKE, A BRAND-NEW
UMBRELLA--YOU’LL LOSE THAT, BUT
NEVER THE OLD, CRAPPY ONE.
>> LOSING AN UMBRELLA’S NOT SO
BAD, BUT A WINNING LOTTERY
TICKET--
>> THAT’S SOMETHING YOU STASH
AWAY AND THEN CAN’T REMEMBER
WHERE.
>> AND WHEN YOU GO LOOK FOR IT
YOU FIND EVERYTHING BUT THAT.
>> MAYBE WE JUST THINK THE STUFF
WE LOSE IS MORE IMPORTANT THAN
THE STUFF WE HAVE.
>> HEY THERE.
>> ARE YOU GUYS LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING?
>> SOMETIMES I WONDER...
WHEN I’M ASLEEP HERE,
MAYBE IT’S ACTUALLY AWAKE OVER
THERE.
AND AS MY MEMORIES GET HAZIER,
I FEEL THAT MY ABILITY TO SENSE
THE PASSING OF TIME HAS BECOME
HAZIER AS WELL.
HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN?
WHEN DID I STOP SEEING MYSELF
WHOLE, EVEN IN DREAMS?
I’M HERE...
AND THERE.
WHEN I’M OVER THERE, WHAT IS THE
WORLD THAT I’M IN?
AND WHAT AM I LOOKING AT?
I HAVE A DREAM THAT RECURS OVER
AND OVER AGAIN.
AND IN MY DREAM, IT’S THIS
QUESTION I’M TRYING TO ANSWER.
[glass shattering]
BUT WHAT I SEE IN THAT DREAM
IS ALWAYS THE SAME.
[screams]
>> HM?
[door opens]
>> CELTY! LISTEN TO THIS.
LAST NIGHT YOU TOLD ME THAT YOU
DIDN’T HAVE TO WORK TODAY,
RIGHT?
SO I JUST LOOKED IT UP.
THIS WILL BE YOUR FIRST DAY OFF
IN THE PAST 265 DAYS!
HM?
HM.
WHAT’S THAT SAD LOOK ABOUT?
>> SOMEHOW HE READS EXPRESSIONS
ON THE FACE I DON’T HAVE.
>> AAH!
>> I HEARD THAT HUMANS HAVE
DREAMS TO ORGANIZE THEIR
MEMORIES.
IS THAT TRUE?
>> WELL, THAT’S CERTAINLY A
SUDDEN QUESTION.
JUST WHAT PURPOSE DO DREAMS
SERVE?
TO PUT IT AS SIMPLY AS POSSIBLE,
WE DON’T KNOW FOR SURE.
THERE ARE CERTAIN AREAS WHERE
MEDICINE STILL HAS A LONG WAY TO
GO.
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT COMES TO UP
HERE.
ALL WE KNOW ABOUT DREAMS IS THAT
IT OCCURS IN THE REM STATE,
A LEVEL OF SLEEP KNOWN AS RAPID
EYE MOVEMENT--
>> HE’S A DOCTOR.
AN UNDERGROUND DOCTOR TO BE
EXACT.
TO BE HONEST, I DON’T REALLY
KNOW ALL THAT HE TRULY DOES.
HE ALLOWS ME TO LIVE HERE WITH
HIM, AND THANKS TO HIS
GENEROSITY I CAN CONTINUE
WORKING IN THIS CITY AS A
TRANSPORTER.
>> SO THEN I GUESS THE REAL
ISSUE IS THAT WE DON’T REALLY
KNOW WHAT A MEMORY IS.
ARE YOU LISTENING?
>> I FEEL VERY GRATEFUL TO HIM.
AND LATELY I’VE COME TO REALIZE
THAT WHAT I FEEL IS MOST LIKELY
LOVE.
BUT...
>> YOU SEEM TO BE DEAD SET ON
THE IDEA THAT YOUR MEMORIES ARE
ONLY CONTAINED IN YOUR HEAD.
BUT WE JUST DON’T KNOW THAT FOR
SURE.
>> OF COURSE THAT’S WHERE THEY
ARE.
>> ENOUGH ABOUT ALL THIS.
COME ON, WHY DON’T WE GET
CHANGED.
WE SHOULD GO AND DO SOMETHING
TODAY.
HM, I’LL TAKE THE DAY OFF WITH
YOU.
SEE? I’M EVEN TURNING OFF MY
PHONE.
[cell phone beeps]
HEY! I’LL CLOSE THE NETWORK TOO!
I’LL PULL THE CORD SO I CAN’T
CHECK EMAIL.
AFTER ALL, THERE’S NO TIME LIKE
THE PRESENT, RIGHT?
SO WHERE SHOULD WE GO?
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT TAKING
YOUR HORSE DOWN TO THE BEACH?
OR MAYBE WE GO TO A HOT SPRINGS.
>> I DON’T WANNA GO ANYWHERE.
>> HOW COME?
>> IF WE’RE TAKING THE DAY OFF,
I’D LIKE TO COOK FOR YOU.
A SORT OF THANK YOU.
>> A HOME-COOKED MEAL?
>> TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT.
WE CAN LOOK FOR A RECIPE.
>> I’M SO MOVED, CELTY!
LET’S SEE, WHAT DO I WANT?
>> I’M SORRY, I OVERSLEPT TODAY.
I GUESS I OWE YOU ONE, MAN.
THANKS FOR THE TEXTBOOK, IT’S A
BIG HELP.
>> NO WORRIES, MY FRIEND.
I FIGURED THE TRIP TO TOKYO
WOULD BEGIN TO WEAR ON YOU
EVENTUALLY.
RIGHT NOW, FOR ALL US PLAYERS
IT’S GAME ON.
COZYING UP TO THE LADIES.
RUBBING SHOULDERS WHILE THE TWO
OF YOU SHARE A TEXTBOOK.
SO WHAT’S THE DEAL, YOU LOSING
THE NECKTIE NOW OR DID YOU
FORGET?
>> HUH?
OH.
>> YOU OKAY?
DID YOU FORGET YOUR WALLET TOO?
>> DON’T TELL ME I--HOW COULD I?
WHERE WAS--OH, NO!
>> YUMMY RUSSIA SUSHI.
>> HEY, SIMON.
>> HM?
>> YOU SEEN YUMATCHI AROUND?
>> OH, KARISAWA, YOU WANT SUSHI?
SORRY, I NO HAVE TODAY.
>> HM, NOT HERE EITHER.
DENGEKI BUNKO’S "ACCEL WORLD"
FINALLY HITS ALL THE STORES
TODAY.
AFTER WE BOTH BOUGHT IT WE WENT
TO GET SOME TEA, THEN SPLIT UP.
AFTER WE LEFT ONE OF THE MAIDS
CHASED ME DOWN.
SHE SAID YUMATCH LEFT HIS CELL
PHONE BEHIND.
>> SO WE LOOK FOR FISH NOW.
>> HUH? THEN DON’T TRY TO GET
CUSTOMERS.
>> PREGO! EXCUSE ME.
WHY YOU NOT A SAY ME WHAT YOU
LOOK FOR?
>> I JUST SAID THAT YUMATCH--
WHO ARE YOU?
"LOST STUFF?"
>> YOU JUST WRITE WHAT YOU LOOK
FOR HERE, AND WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE YOU FIND IT.
YOU CAN A TELL ME.
>> WOW, THIS IS SO AWESOME,
I LOVE IT.
ARE YOU GONNA BE HERE ALL DAY?
>> SI, I ASKING A EVERYONE IN
AREA.
>> [heavy breathing]
MY PHONE!
>> both: HUH? WELCOME HOME,
MASTER.
>> I WONDER WHAT IT IS I’M
LOOKING FOR?
KAZUTANO’S SAFE, AND I SHOULD
LEAVE IT AT THAT.
I EVEN TOLD WALKER AND ERIKA
THAT I WOULD LET IT GO.
BUT FOR SOME REASON I CAN’T.
WHAT ARE YOU HIDING IN THERE?
THEY SAY YAGIRI PHARMACEUTICALS
IS SECRETLY TIED TO THE AWAKUSU.
OR MAYBE THE NORTH AMERICAN
NEBRA CORP.
BUT STANDING HERE LEANING ON
THIS TREE ISN’T GONNA HELP ME
FIND WHAT I’M LOOKING FOR.
>> [panting]
HEY, SIMON, YOU SEEN ERIKA?
>> TODAY NO HAVE.
>> MAN.
>> WHO WANT EAT A DELICIOUS
RUSSIA SUSHI?
>> HUH?
WOW! WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
CELTY, LET’S JUST USE A NORMAL
KNIFE, OKAY?
WOW, THIS IS GREAT, REALLY
GREAT.
THIS IS SO GOOD.
>> WAIT, WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
>> UH, AM I REALLY?
OH, I’M JUST SO IMPRESSED BY
YOU.
THIS IS REALLY WONDERFUL.
THE SUPER-SWEET SAUTéED VEGGIES,
WITH THE SALTY-BITTER MISO SOUP.
>> SOMETHING’S WRONG.
>> NO, YOUR COOKING IS
DISTINCTIVE AND UNORTHODOX.
IN FACT IT’S JUST LIKE YOU ARE.
>> THAT ISN’T A COMPLIMENT.
I GET IT, I SCREWED UP AGAIN.
IT’S FINE, DON’T FORCE YOURSELF
TO EAT IT.
>> BUT I’M NOT FORCING MYSELF,
IT REALLY IS QUITE GOOD.
AAH--
>> I SAID DON’T EAT IT!
>> AAH--
>> UH, HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HUH, HOW DOES THIS WORK ANYWAY?
LISTEN, I MEAN IT, YOU REALLY
ARE A VERY GOOD COOK.
WHO CARES IF YOU DON’T HAVE A
TRUE SENS DE GOUT.
>> SENS DE WHAT?
>> IT MEANS SENSE OF TASTE.
SEE, IF YOUR DNA IS LACKING A
SENSE OF TASTE, YOUR BRAIN WON’T
PROCESS IT AT ALL.
BUT YOU DON’T HAVE TO EAT, SO
ALL THIS IS IRRELEVANT.
SO DON’T WORRY ABOUT IT.
COME ON, CHEER UP, WILL YA?
HEY, WHAT DO YOU SAY WE PLAY A
GAME?
>> DON’T TREAT ME LIKE A CHILD,
IT’LL JUST IRRITATE ME MORE.
>> I’M NOT, CELTY.
>> I ADMIT, MOST OF MY MEMORIES
COME FROM THE YEARS I’VE SPENT
LIVING WITH YOU.
BUT SOME OF MY FOGGY MEMORIES
ARE OVER 100 YEARS OLD.
AND I KNOW MY HEAD HAS MORE.
>> DO YOU REALLY NEED MEMORIES
FROM HUNDREDS OF YEARS AGO?
>> WELL, WHAT ARE YOU GETTING
AT?
>> LOOK, IT’S LIKE I’M ALWAYS
SAYING--YOU’RE NOT MISSING
ANYTHING, YOU’RE FINE THE WAY
YOU ARE.
>> WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
I’M FORGETTING MY OWN FACE!
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT FEELS
LIKE?
>> WAIT, DON’T GO!
I’M SORRY!
[doorbell rings]
CELTY!
YOU CAME BACK!
>> YOU’VE GOTTA KEEP YOUR PHONE
ON, DOC.
THERE’S SOMEONE WE NEED YOU TO
FIX UP RIGHT AWAY.
>> HM.
>> HEY, ANRI, SOMETHING WRONG?
>> THEY’RE GONE AGAIN.
>> GONE?
>> UH-OH! WHAT’D YOU FORGET THIS
TIME, MIKADO?
>> IT’S ANRI, HER SHOES ARE
GONE.
>> AGAIN?
MAN, PEOPLE NEED TO GET A LIFE.
I THINK THAT I MIGHT HAVE AN
IDEA WHO’S BEHIND ALL THIS.
>> MASAOMI?
>> GOTTA GO.
>> HEY, WAIT, WHERE ARE YOU GO--
[sighs]
>> MASAOMI WAS A LITTLE SCARY
JUST NOW.
IT WAS ALMOST AS IF HE WAS A
DIFFERENT PERSON.
>> YOU THINK SO?
I CAN’T BELIEVE THAT HE JUST
LEFT US.
I MEAN, WHAT’S THE RUSH?
>> YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS A KID
I USED TO LOSE THINGS ALL THE
TIME.
I’D BREAK DOWN AND START CRYING
"I CAN’T FIND IT, I CAN’T FIND
IT."
AND THAT’S WHEN MY MOM WOULD
SHOW UP AND HELP LOOK FOR IT.
>> YOUR MOM SOUNDS LIKE SHE’S
PRETTY NICE.
>> YEAH, BOTH MY MOM AND DAD ARE
REALLY NICE.
OH.
>> OH.
>> WE CAN STOP, IT’S FINE.
I’LL JUST WEAR THESE HOME.
THANKS FOR HELPING ME LOOK,
MIKADO, I APPRECIATE YOU TRYING
TO HELP.
>> UH, BUT...
YOU CAN STOP LOOKING, MASAOMI.
DON’T WORRY ABOUT WHO DID IT.
NOT EXACTLY, SHE JUST DECIDED
TO GO ON HOME.
HUH? NO, I HAVE NO IDEA.
ME? WELL, I’M STILL LOOKING OF
COURSE.
ALL RIGHT, SEE YOU TOMORROW.
THERE THEY ARE!
>> WHAT AM I DOING?
>> SEE? THAT’S WEIRD, ISN’T IT?
I DON’T REMEMBER WHAT WAS HERE
AT ALL.
EMPTY LOTS KIND OF TRIP ME OUT.
ONCE THEY TEAR IT ALL DOWN IT’S
HARD TO REMEMBER WHAT WAS THERE.
SOMETHING USED TO BE HERE,
RIGHT?
I MEAN, LIKE SOMETHING BIG.
HM.
>> WHAT AM I THINKING?
I GET ANNOYED WHEN SHINRA TELLS
ME TO LET IT GO AND STOP LOOKING
FOR MY HEAD.
BUT LOOK AT ME.
HERE I AM WITH A JOB AND MAKING
FRIENDS.
IT’S LIKE I’VE STARTED THINKING
I’M A HUMAN.
>> ANYWAY, YOU SAID YOU HAD
SOMETHING YOU WANTED TO TALK TO
ME ABOUT.
WHAT WAS IT?
>> I REMEMBER!
IT WAS A LONG, SKINNY BLUE
BUILDING, RIGHT?
OH, YEAH, THAT OLD CRAPPY ONE.
THERE WAS AN OLD LADY ON THE
FIRST FLOOR WHO SOLD CIGARETTES.
WAY TO GO, TRANSPORTER.
>> I KNOW MY HEAD IS IN THIS
TOWN, I CAN FEEL IT.
BUT...
>> HUH?
>> BONGIORNO, HOW ARE YOU?
>> UH, ME?
>> I LOOKED FOR SOMETHING
BEAUTIFUL AND HOPING IN
JAPANESE.
GO ON, WHY YOU NOT WRITE DOWN
WHAT YOU LOOKING FOR DEEP DOWN
IN YOUR HEART?
>> OH, WELL, I, UH...
YOU KNOW, WOULD YOU MIND IF I
TOOK A LOOK AT THAT?
>> OKAY.
>> OH.
WONDER IF SHE FOUND HIM?
TODAY I ENDED UP LOOKING FOR ALL
KINDS OF STUFF.
BUT I FOUND SOME STUFF AND
DIDN’T FIND SOME STUFF.
[knock on door]
>> HIS BAG WAS GONE SO I ASSUMED
HE WAS ON A JOB.
BUT SOMETHING JUST DIDN’T FEEL
RIGHT.
>> FIREWORKS?
>> YEAH, HE WENT ON QUITE A
RAMPAGE.
IT TOOK SEVERAL OF OUR GUYS TO
TAKE HIM DOWN.
>> ALL FOR FIREWORKS?
>> SEEMS TO ME LIKE YOUR STAFF
GOT A LITTLE OUT OF HAND.
>> WELL, HE CAUSED QUITE A
SCENE.
KEPT SPOUTING SOME GIBBERISH
ABOUT HOW HIS GIRLFRIEND WAS
KIDNAPPED AND THE ONLY THING
SHE REMEMBERS FROM THAT NIGHT
WAS THIS PLACE.
THEN HE DEMANDED WE TELL HIM
WHAT WE DID TO HER.
>> HE WASN’T SPOUTING GIBBERISH,
HE WAS TELLING THE TRUTH.
>> ANYWAY, DOC, THINK YOU CAN
FIX IT? MAKE IT SO THAT HE
DOESN’T REMEMBER THIS PLACE WHEN
HE WAKES UP?
THAT’S ALL THAT WE’RE ASKING OF
YOU, OKAY?
>> THERE’S NO EASY WAY TO DO
THAT, MEMORIES ARE A TRICKY
THING TO GET RID OF.
AND PLUS, I’LL REMEMBER THIS
KID.
>> LISTEN, WE ARE GONNA RELEASE
HIM, BUT WHETHER HE WILL GO HOME
OR NOT I’M NOT SO SURE.
ALL RIGHT, LET’S BE CLEAR,
DOCTOR.
THE CHIEF AND I BOTH TRUST YOU
COMPLETELY.
AFTER ALL, YOU ARE KEEPING THAT
THING A SECRET.
OH, AND BY THE WAY, THAT
ROOMMATE YOU HAVE, SHE IS MORE
THAN JUST YOUR AVERAGE
HOUSEGUEST, ISN’T SHE?
>> AT THAT MOMENT MY FOCUS
SHIFTED.
I WASN’T THINKING ABOUT MY HEAD,
NOR THE CENTURY WORTH OF
DULLAHAN MEMORIES THAT LIVE
INSIDE IT.
I WASN’T THINKING OF ANYTHING...
EXCEPT THAT.
>> HEY, WILL YOU COME EAT WITH
ME?
THE RESTAURANT WON’T COMPLAIN
IF I ORDER DINNER FOR TWO.
I KNOW A REALLY GREAT PLACE.
PLEASE, CELTY.
TO BE HONEST, I HATE EATING BY
MYSELF.
WHAT IS THIS CONVOLUTED
MYSTERY FOOD IN FRONT OF ME?
>> FRIED CHICKEN SUSHI, CHEESE
SUSHI, MABO SUSHI, PROSCIUTTO
SUSHI, AND THIS...
THIS SOUR CREAM SUSHI.
>> NONE OF THIS SHOULD EVER BE
SUSHI!
>> WHY IT WRONG? IT IS SPECIAL
PLATE, AND IT GOOD PRICE!
>> THEY’RE SERVING FORTUNE
COOKIES FOR DESSERT?
COME ON, YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
YOU’VE SEEN THESE BEFORE, RIGHT?
THERE’S A PIECE OF PAPER INSIDE
THAT TELLS YOU A FORTUNE.
LET’S SEE WHAT IT SAYS.
THIS ONE’S YOURS.
LET ME SEE.
HM.
WELL, ACCORDING TO YOUR FORTUNE,
YOU’RE GOING TO FIND WHAT YOU’RE
LOOKING FOR.
MM, EASY.
I’M NOT USED TO YOU BEING SO
HAPPY.
>> I’M VERY HAPPY, SHINRA.
>> OH.
>> SO WHAT DOES YOURS SAY?
>> UM...
[chewing]
MY COOKIE DIDN’T HAVE A FORTUNE.
>> AS I AM NOW, I CAN’T CRY.
[laughing and singing]
>> I DON’T KNOW, WHEN I’M SAD
HERE IS IT SOBBING SOMEWHERE
ELSE?
>> OH.
>> HM.
>> THANKS A LOT.
>> OH.
>> REGARDLESS...
I HOPE WHEREVER IT IS...
IT’S SMILING.
>> HM.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> MM.
>> YOU’RE STILL SCARED.
NO ONE’S HERE, WE’RE TOTALLY
ALONE.
HEY, WHAT’S WRONG?
CAN YOU REMEMBER ANYTHING YET?
>> MM.
>> MM, IT’S ALL RIGHT.
THAT ISN’T IMPORTANT TO ME.
I TOLD YOU BEFORE, I DON’T
CARE ABOUT YOUR PAST, JUST OUR
FUTURE.
JUST AS YOU ARE NOW.
TOGETHER, WE ARE THE FUTURE.
>> [cries]
>> I DO LOVE YOU, CELTY.
>> THAT NIGHT, FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN YEARS, I HAD A DREAM OF
WHEN I WAS WHOLE.
[horses neighing]
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> MY LOVE IS DIFFERENT.
IT’S NOT THE KIND OF LOVE THAT
IS ALWAYS IN NEED,
ALWAYS LOOKING.
IT’S MORE PERFECT THAN THAT.
NEXT TIME, LOVE AND CHERISH.
WHAT SEIJI NEEDS IS ME.