[Uragiri no Yuyake
by Theater Brook]
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> BUT FOR ME, THIS IS A SURE
SIGN SHE’S TURNING INTO A REAL
BIRI BIRI HEROINE.
>> AAH!
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> SAVE ME!
>> HOW DO YOU INTEND TO GET YOUR
HEAD BACK, ANYWAY?
IT’S ATTACHED TO ANOTHER BODY.
>> I NEED TO SEE THIS GIRL,
NO MATTER WHAT.
>> CHANCES ARE PRETTY GOOD
YAGIRI PHARMACEUTICALS SENT
THEM.
>> YOUR BIG SIS WILL HANDLE IT
ALL, OKAY?
>> HONESTLY, I ONLY HALF
BELIEVED THIS WAS TRUE.
>> ALL RIGHT, I THINK ALL MY
CARDS ARE IN ORDER NOW.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
[wind blowing]
>> I HAVE TO GO.
I HAVE TO GO AND GET HER BACK.
MY SISTER CAN’T DO IT.
I HAVE TO DO IT.
I HAVE TO DO IT MYSELF.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, SHE WASN’T
THERE?
>> CORRECT.
IT SEEMS BY THE TIME THEY
ARRIVED, SHE HAD ALREADY LEFT.
>> AND THE STUDENT WHO LIVED
THERE?
WHAT WAS HIS NAME...
RYUGAMINE?
WHERE IS HE?
>> WHEN THE KID CAME BACK, THEY
GRILLED HIM PRETTY HARD.
APPARENTLY, THEY WERE ABOUT TO
THROW HIM IN THE VAN AND BRING
HIM HERE.
BUT THEN HIS FRIENDS SHOWED UP.
>> [scoffs] SO WHAT!
YOU SHOULD HAVE JUST BROUGHT HIS
FRIENDS IN AS WELL.
YOU’RE USELESS.
>> WHAT’S OUR NEXT STEP?
>> [sighs]
[telephone rings]
HMM?
HELLO?
>> IS THIS MISS NAMIE YAGIRI?
>> WITH WHOM AM I SPEAKING?
>> MY NAME IS MIKADO RYUGAMINE.
>> UH...
>> WOULD YOU LIKE TO MAKE A
TRADE?
[wind blowing]
[indistinct chatter]
>> HUH?
>> HMM? HUH?
>> MAN, I’M STARVING.
>> ♪ WHOO-HOO-HOO ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
>> WELCOME. WELCOME.
WANT RUSSIA SUSHI?
IT GOOD. IT CHEAP.
>> WHAT’S THE MEANING OF LIFE?
WHAT’S THE REASON WE’RE HERE?
SOME GUY ASKED ME THAT ONCE AND
I RESPONDED BY PUMMELING HIS
PATHETIC ASS TO CHUM!
I GET AN EMO KID IN JUNIOR HIGH
ASKING THAT, BUT A 20-SOMETHING
YAKUZA?
THAT’S JUST WRONG.
>> I SEE.
>> HEY, SIMON, COME CLEAN.
YOU’RE NOT GETTING A SINGLE WORD
OF THIS, ARE YOU?
>> HMM, I SEE. VERY TRUE.
>> UH--UNH...
>> AAH!
>> I’VE BEEN IN THIS CITY FOR 20
YEARS NOW.
AFTER ALL THIS TIME, HAVE I
CHANGED?
>> IT WASN’T A WASTE OF TIME.
THE 20 YEARS YOU’VE LIVED HERE
WERE WELL SPENT.
USE WHAT YOU’VE LEARNED GOING
FORWARD, AND YOU’LL SEE YOUR
LIFE HAS PURPOSE HERE.
>> USE WHAT I’VE LEARNED?
AND HOW WOULD I GO ABOUT DOING
THAT?
>> FOR STARTERS, YOU COULD MARRY
ME.
>> SHINRA...
[tires screech]
>> MOVE IT.
>> UGH!
>> ARE YOU MIKADO?
>> OH.
>> [chuckles]
YOU’RE A MUCH QUIETER KID THAN I
HAD EXPECTED YOU TO BE.
WELL, MAYBE THESE DAYS, KIDS
LIKE YOU ARE THE SCARY ONES.
[indistinct chatter]
>> UH.
>> SO WHAT’S THIS TRADE YOU
MENTIONED?
>> UH...
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I CAN TELL YOU
WHERE TO FIND THE GIRL THAT
YOU’RE LOOKING FOR.
>> I SEE.
AND WHAT’S YOUR PRICE?
>> NO, I DON’T WANT YOUR MONEY.
>> THEN WHAT, EXACTLY, DO YOU
WANT?
>> I WANT THE TRUTH.
>> [chuckles] TRUTH?
I DON’T KNOW WHAT YOU’RE TALKING
ABOUT.
>> I THINK YOU DO.
ALL I’M ASKING IS FOR YOU TO
TELL THE TRUTH ABOUT WHAT YOUR
BROTHER DID TO MIKA HARIMA, AND
ABOUT WHAT YOU DID TO MIKA’S
BODY.
UNFORTUNATELY, ALL MY EVIDENCE
IS CIRCUMSTANTIAL.
I’LL BE MORE DIRECT.
TURN YOURSELVES IN.
>> [chuckles]
SO THAT’S THE KIND OF YOUNG MAN
YOU ARE.
WELL...
IF YOU IMPEDED MY BROTHER IN ANY
WAY, I WILL NEVER FORGIVE YOU.
ANYONE WHO DOES THAT IS
OBVIOUSLY WRONG.
AND I WON’T ALLOW THEM TO EXIST!
>> OH...I SEE.
SO THAT’S...THE KIND OF PERSON
SHE IS.
>> HEY, TELL ME, WHERE CAN I
FIND MY SISTER?
I HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE.
THAT GIRL NEEDS ME.
I HAVE TO BE THERE FOR HER!
>> [sighs]
>> COME ON!
TELL ME WHERE SHE IS!
>> SO THAT’S WHY SHE DID IT.
BECAUSE OF HER TWISTED LOGIC,
ONE PERSON DIED AND ANOTHER WAS
HORRIBLY DISFIGURED.
NOW SHE’S AFTER ME.
[shudders]
[sighs]
[grunts]
AND THIS IS THE REASON YOU TOY
WITH PEOPLE.
DO YOU INTEND TO MAKE SEIJI’S
LIFE MISERABLE NOW JUST FOR YOUR
OWN SELF-GAIN?
>> THIS IS THE QUESTION YOU ASK?
IF A BOY YOUR AGE SUDDENLY GETS
WRAPPED UP IN THE UNDERWORLD,
AND ALL HE CAN DO IS...
>> THIS’LL WORK, RIGHT?
>> THEN HE SHOULD LEARN TO SHUT
HIS MOUTH.
>> MAYBE IT WAS CLICHE AND
SIMPLE, BUT SO WHAT!
WHO CARES?
SOMEONE LIKE YOU MAY NEED
CLICHES.
AFTER ALL, YOU CAN’T UNDERSTAND
THE SIMPLE FACT THAT MURDER IS
WRONG!
>> YOU WATCH TOO MUCH TV.
THIS ISN’T A SCRIPTED SHOW
WRITTEN BY SOME HACK.
YOU’RE PLAYING FOR REAL NOW.
>> IT’S GONNA BE OKAY.
>> YOU’RE NOT IN A TV SHOW OR
MOVIE.
YOU DON’T HAVE THE STARRING ROLE
HERE, SO KNOW YOUR PLACE!
>> AND JUST WHAT’S WRONG WITH
THAT?
WITH CLICHES? THE EXPECTED?
I LOVE THAT!
I LOVE TIRED OLD STORIES AND
HAPPY ENDINGS.
WHAT’S SO WRONG ABOUT WANTING
THAT?
I’M NOT GOING TO TELL YOU I’M
DOING THIS FOR HUMANITY OR FOR
THE SAKE OF THE WORLD.
I JUST WANT TO SEE IF IT’S TRUE.
BECAUSE I BELIEVE IT IS.
THAT’S RIGHT, I BELIEVE.
I BELIEVE IN THEM.
[indistinct chatter]
THEY’LL DO IT. I KNOW IT.
YOU’RE RIGHT, MY IDEALS ARE
PRETTY CONVENTIONAL.
BUT THAT’S JUST ANOTHER WAY OF
SAYING WHAT I BELIEVE--
EXACTLY WHAT THE MAJORITY OF
PEOPLE BELIEVE TOO!
[shudders]
>> HMM.
IS THAT ALL YOU HAD TO SAY?
ARE YOU DONE?
>> YOU REFUSE TO LISTEN TO
REASON, AND I’D HAVE NO LUCK
AGAINST YOU JUST BY MYSELF.
YOU WON’T EVEN GIVE ME THE TIME
TO TRY.
THAT’S WHY...
I’LL RELY ON NUMBERS!
[beep]
[beep beep]
[electronic tone]
>> [chuckles]
[cell phone chimes]
>> YOU’VE GOT MAIL.
[cell phones ringing, chiming]
[alarmed gasps]
>> [gasps] WHAT?
[cell phones chiming, ringing]
[tires screech]
>> CHECK IT OUT!
IS EVERYONE HERE IN ON THIS?
>> AWESOME!
THIS IS SO COOL.
IT’S LIKE THEY LIFTED IT
STRAIGHT OUT OF MISSING!
[phone messages in Japanese]
>> IT’S HERE!
>> YOU GUYS SHITTIN’ ME?
[melodic ringtone]
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN...
SABURO, YOU TAKE IT FROM HERE.
>> UH, SURE.
>> LET’S GO.
[cell phones ringing, chiming]
>> YO.
[cell phone rings]
>> HMM?
>> [gasps]
UH...
[cell phones ringing, chiming]
[door shuts]
[footsteps]
[wind blowing]
>> OH...
>> HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE THERE?
>> THIS IS SO RAD.
IT’S OUR FIRST MEETING EVER, AND
LOOK AT THE TURNOUT WE GOT.
IT’S CRAZY HUGE!
>> THIS IS IT?
THIS IS THE DOLLARS?
[cell phones ringing, chiming]
>> UNH...
[cell phone rings]
HUH?
>> HUH? HUH?
HEY, ISAAC?
>> WHAT IS IT, MIRIA?
>> ALL THESE PEOPLE WHO SHOWED
UP HERE, THEY’RE ALL PART OF THE
DOLLARS, RIGHT?
>> YEP!
DAMN STRAIGHT, MIRIA.
>> WOW!
>> HERE’S THE LOWDOWN,
HONEYBUNCH!
AS OF RIGHT NOW, WE’RE
OFFICIALLY PART OF THIS GROUP OF
HEPCATS EVERYONE’S TALKING
ABOUT!
>> WHAT IS THIS?
THEY CAN’T--
ARE THEY ALL REALLY--
NO, THIS CAN’T BE!
>> REALLY?
EVERYONE JUST MET FOR THE FIRST
TIME TODAY?
OH, MY GOSH, THIS IS SO COOL!
SO COOL! SO COOL!
SO COOL!
[jet roars across the sky]
>> BACK HOME, THE SKY WAS BIG
AND VAST.
BUT THERE WAS NOTHING THERE.
[rooster crows]
[bicycle bell chimes]
[children laughing]
WHEN I WAS A KID, MY TOWN SEEMED
LIKE IT WAS FILLED WITH
ADVENTURE.
WHEN DID THAT CHANGE?
WHEN DID I START FEELING LIKE
THIS?
I WANTED TO CHANGE THINGS, BUT I
HAD NO REASON TO LEAVE, OR EVEN
THE COURAGE TO DO IT.
AND THEN ONE DAY...
UNH...UNH!
UHH...
WOW. HMM.
MM...HMM.
OKAY, TWICE AND...
SUDDENLY THERE WERE ALL THESE
DIFFERENT WORLDS OUT THERE.
WORLDS I’D NEVER SEEN OR TALKED
TO.
MASAOMI HAD MOVED TO TOKYO BY
THEN, AND WE STARTED EMAILING.
AH...
I MADE SOME NEW FRIENDS TOO.
AND THEN ONE DAY, I HAD AN IDEA.
IT STARTED OUT MORE AS A JOKE
THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
[chuckles]
>> A GANG?
>> YEAH, THAT’S WHAT I’M
THINKING.
I’VE HEARD THERE’S A WHOLE LOT
OF ’EM IN TOKYO RIGHT NOW.
>> ARE YOU SAYING YOU WANT TO
MAKE AN ONLINE GANG?
>> NO, THAT’S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
I WANT PEOPLE TO THINK THIS ONE
IS REAL.
WE’LL JUST SAY THE GANG IS IN
IKEBUKURO, AND WE’LL SPREAD THE
RUMOR ALL OVER THE INTERNET.
NONE OF US EVER REVEALED THAT WE
WERE PART OF THE DOLLARS.
WE TOLD PEOPLE THAT WE’D HEARD
THE RUMOR FROM SOMEWHERE ELSE,
AND PRETTY SOON IT WAS
EVERYWHERE.
WE MADE A WEB SITE FOR THE GANG,
ONE YOU CAN ONLY ACCESS WITH A
PASSWORD.
THEN WE RANDOMLY LEAKED THE
PASSWORD IN EMAILS AND FORUMS.
I EVEN CREATED A BUNCH OF POSTS
ON OUR MESSAGE BOARD AS OTHER
MEMBERS.
OF COURSE, A LOT OF PEOPLE
DIDN’T BELIEVE US.
BUT AFTER A WHILE, PEOPLE
STARTED TO STICK UP FOR US.
EVERYONE WAS HAPPY.
>> DUDE, EVERYONE’S BUYING IT.
>> I KNOW. THEY’RE ALL IDIOTS.
>> BUT I HAD A BAD FEELING.
PEOPLE STARTED APPEARING IN THE
REAL WORLD SAYING THEY WERE IN
THE DOLLARS.
THAT’S NOT ALL.
OUR MEMBER COUNT WAS REALLY
SKYROCKETING...
EVEN THOUGH WE’D LONG STOPPED
GIVING OUT THE PASSWORD.
IT WAS LIKE SOMEONE ELSE WAS
LEAKING IT FOR US.
HEY, GUYS, ARE YOU THERE?
HELLO?
MAYBE THEY GOT SCARED, BUT THE
GUYS WHO HELPED ME START THE
DOLLARS HAD VANISHED.
EVEN THOUGH THEY LEFT, I KEPT
WITH IT.
TRUTH IS, I COULDN’T STOP.
MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE WALKED AWAY
THEN, BUT I DIDN’T.
NO, THAT ISN’T TRUE.
I KNOW THERE’S BEEN SOME BAD
PEOPLE, BUT MOST OF THE PEOPLE
IN THE GROUP ARE GOOD.
I KNOW IT.
WHY DON’T WE MAKE THE DOLLARS
DIFFERENT FROM THE OTHER GANGS?
LET’S MAKE IT A GOOD ONE.
LET’S ALWAYS DO WHAT’S RIGHT SO
WE NEGATE ALL THE BAD
IMPRESSIONS ALL THE OTHER GANGS
HAVE LEFT BEHIND.
UH...EHH...
LIKE PICKING UP GARBAGE OR
ERASING GRAFFITI.
YOU KNOW, STUFF LIKE THAT.
[sighs]
>> THAT’S RIGHT, THE ENTIRE
NEIGHBORHOOD IS COMPLETELY
MYSTIFIED.
SOMETIME DURING THE COURSE OF
LAST NIGHT, THE LARGE AMOUNT OF
GRAFFITI THAT HAD STAINED THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD’S WALL SUDDENLY
DISAPPEARED BY THIS MORNING.
IT’S HARD TO BELIEVE THAT ONE
PERSON COULD HAVE REMOVED SO
MUCH GRAFFITI.
AT THIS JUNCTURE, NO ONE...
>> [nervous chuckle]
NO, THIS CAN’T BE.
MASAOMI INVITED ME TO TOKYO, AND
I CAME.
AND THEN...
THE DOLLARS?
>> I DON’T MUCH ABOUT ’EM.
ALL’S I KNOW IS THERE’S A LOT OF
’EM.
I ALSO HEARD THEY’RE KIND OF
CRAZY.
I WOULD JUST STAY AWAY FROM THEM
IF I WAS YOU.
THEY’RE SORT OF LIKE A COLOR
GANG, BUT NO ONE KNOWS WHAT
COLOR THEY ARE.
>> I WOULDN’T TRY AND GET NEAR
THEM JUST FOR KICKS.
THE LESS YOU KNOW ABOUT THOSE
GUYS, THE BETTER.
>> WOULDN’T YOU GUYS SAY THE
DOLLARS ARE PRETTY HARDCORE
RIGHT NOW?
>> WHAT ARE THE DOLLARS LIKE?
FILL US IN.
>> WELL, I GUESS I’D SAY
TRANSPARENT, AS IN NO COLOR.
>> [slurps]
THE DOLLARS?
YEAH, I KNOW ’EM.
IN FACT, I’M ONE OF ’EM.
>> ONCE I JOINED THE DOLLARS,
I GOT A GIRLFRIEND.
>> IT’S PRETTY COOL.
POST SOMETHING RANDOM ON THEIR
SITE...
>> AND NO MATTER WHAT, SOMEONE
ALWAYS RESPONDS.
>> YOU KNOW, AT THIS AGE,
MEETING SOMEONE OUTSIDE OF WORK
IS OTHERWISE IMPOSSIBLE.
>> DID YOU HEAR?
THIS DUDE WAS ABOUT TO GET
SNATCHED BY THOSE HUMAN
TRAFFICKER GUYS, AND THE DOLLARS
TOTALLY SAVED HIM!
THE DOLLARS FREAKIN’ ROCK!
>> I DON’T KNOW, IT SEEMED COOL,
SO WHY NOT?
[jet engine roars]
[cell phones ringing, chiming]
>> [chuckles]
THIS IS SO MUCH FUN.
WHO WOULD HAVE GUESSED?
[laughs]
GOOD TIMES, RIGHT?
>> WHAT IS...GOING ON?
WHAT IS THIS?
WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE?
>> HEY, DO YOU THINK WHOEVER
STARTED THE DOLLARS IS HERE?
YOU SEE AN ARABIAN OIL SHEIK
ANYWHERE?
>> UH-UH. NOWHERE.
HEY, SABURO, THE GUY WHO SENT US
THAT MESSAGE IS THE GUY WHO
ACTUALLY STARTED THE DOLLARS,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH, THAT’S WHAT I HEARD.
[tires screech]
>> THAT’S A RED LIGHT!
RED LIGHT! RED LIGHT!
>> [gasps]
[all shout]
[tires screech]
>> [sighs]
SHE’S NOT SAYING A WORD.
>> HUH?
DOTACHIN! DOTACHIN!
>> I SAID DON’T CALL ME THAT.
>> LOOK, THERE’S A RESPONSE
ON THE DOLLARS’ MESSAGE BOARD.
>> EVERYTHING IS IN PLACE NOW.
I’M GONNA LET YOU MEET HER.
HOWEVER, FIRST I NEED YOU TO DO
ME A BIG FAVOR.
[wind blowing]
>> CELTY.
>> WHERE’D HE GO?
WHAT ARE YOU JUST STANDING THERE
FOR?
FIND HIM AND BRING HIM BACK!
>> RIGHT! ON IT!
>> MOVE IT!
>> OUT OF THE WAY.
>> HEY, WATCH IT!
>> OH...
[gasps]
[all gasping]
>> UNH! SCREW IT!
>> UH...WHO SAID THAT?
>> THAT’S RIGHT, I HAVE NO HEAD.
I’M A MONSTER.
I HAVE NO MOUTH TO SPEAK MY
THOUGHTS OR EYES TO CONVEY MY
EMOTIONS.
>> ARE YOU HEARING THAT?
>> WHO’S SAYING IT?
>> BUT SO WHAT!
WHO GIVES A DAMN?
I DON’T CARE ANYMORE!
>> OH...CELTY.
[alarmed cries]
[tires screech]
>> I AM HERE, AND I AM REAL.
>> WHO THE HELL--
[grunts and groans]
>> IF YOU SAY I HAVE NO EYES,
THEN WATCH MY ACTIONS VERY
CLOSELY.
>> UNH!
>> LISTEN TO THE CRIES OF THOSE
AROUND YOU--
THE ONES WHO’VE ANGERED THIS
MONSTER!
>> UNH!
[alarmed murmurs]
>> [gasps]
>> OH...
>> UH...
>> [chuckles]
[wind blowing]
[alarmed murmurs]
>> IT’S--IT’S THE HEADLESS
RIDER.
>> THE HEADLESS RIDER?
>> HEADLESS RIDER?
>> THAT’S RIGHT, I’M HERE.
RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU.
TAKE A LOOK.
DO YOU HEAR ME SCREAMING?
THIS IS MY MOMENT.
THIS IS MY TIME TO BE BORN!
I AM INJECTING MY VERY EXISTENCE
INTO THE VEINS OF THIS CITY!
[alarmed cries and shouts]
>> ARE YOU MIKADO RYUGAMINE?
>> HUH? OH...
>> WHERE’S CELTY?
I WANT CELTY!
GIVE HER BACK!
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> THAT’S RIGHT.
I FOUND SOMETHING IN THIS CITY
THAT IS GENUINELY TRUE.
IT’S SO SIMPLE AND ORDINARY THAT
IT’S HARD TO BELIEVE.
I THINK THAT BOY HAS FOUND IT,
TOO.
NEXT TIME, YIN AND YANG.