[Uragiri no Yuyake
by Theater Brook]
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> I HAVE MY REASONS.
THIS IS SOMETHING VERY IMPORTANT
TO ME.
>> I’M FORGETTING MY OWN FACE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT FEELS
LIKE?
>> HEY, MISS?
>> AAH!
>> HEY!
>> YAGIRI PHARMA, HUH?
>> YOU GUYS REALLY THINK THAT’S
TRUE, THEY EXPERIMENT ON HUMANS
IN THERE?
>> THAT’S NOT MIKA HARIMA.
>> OF COURSE, DEAR.
YOU CAN TAKE ALL THE MONEY YOU
WANT.
IT’S NO PROBLEM.
>> WE ARE THE FUTURE.
I DO LOVE YOU, CELTY.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
>> EVERYONE IS FAKE.
THE WORLD’S FILLED WITH THESE
PEOPLE.
THEY SAY THEY LOVE AND ADORE
YOU, BUT ALL THEY REALLY WANT TO
DO IS POSSESS YOU.
THEY WANT YOU TO NEED THEM AND
BE THERE FOR THEM.
>> YOU’VE REACHED THE VOICE
MAIL BOX OF...
>> ALWAYS TAKING.
NEVER GIVING ANYTHING IN RETURN.
MY LOVE IS DIFFERENT.
IT’S GREATER AND MORE PERFECT.
>> YEAH. YEAH, I KNOW, SIS.
OKAY. THANKS FOR THE CASH.
I’LL SEE YOU.
ARE YOU THIRSTY?
WANT ME TO GET YOU A DRINK?
LOOK, THERE’S A VENDING MACHINE
RIGHT OVER THERE.
I’LL BE RIGHT BACK.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU...
YOU’RE SO CUTE.
>> YOUR MEN STILL HAVEN’T FOUND
THEM.
>> NO.
SORRY, WE’RE TRYING OUR BEST.
>> SO WHAT HAPPENED TO THE GUY
THAT YOU HAD TAILING THEM?
>> I JUST HAD A CONVERSATION
WITH HIM.
THEY WERE IN THE SAME HOTEL FOR
THE PAST FEW DAYS, BUT SEIJI GOT
BY HIM LAST NIGHT AND ENDED UP
CHANGING HOTELS.
>> WELL, HE WAS STILL ANSWERING
HIS CELL LAST NIGHT AROUND 7:00.
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS TO HIM...
>> I THINK WE’RE GOING TO BE
OKAY.
HE PROMISED US THAT HE WOULDN’T
LEAVE IKEBUKURO.
WE WILL FIND HIM, DON’T WORRY.
>> LISTEN, IF THE POLICE COME
ACROSS THAT THING BEFORE WE DO,
THAT WON’T WORK OUT WELL FOR US.
>> UM--WELL, I JUST--
>> [sighs] THIS IS ABSURD.
I CAN’T WAIT FOR YOU PEOPLE TO
GET IT RIGHT.
>> BUT CHIEF--
>> DON’T WORRY.
I WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
IT WAS JUST A DOLL TO ME,
NOTHING MORE.
A BEAUTIFUL, EXPENSIVE DOLL LIKE
MY UNCLE USED TO BRING ME FROM
THE FOREIGN COUNTRIES HE
VISITED.
BUT I’VE NEVER LIKED DOLLS, EVEN
AS A CHILD.
I WAS NEVER SURE WHY HE GAVE ME
THE DOLLS HE DID.
I SOMETIMES WONDER IF HE BOUGHT
THE ONES HE LIKED AND SENT THEM
ON TO ME, WITH NO THOUGHT FOR
WHAT I WOULD LIKE.
OH...HMM?
HEY, SEIJI, LOOK!
>> HUH?
>> PRETTY, HUH?
>> [babbling]
>> [giggles]
OH, WHAT’S THIS?
THAT HOUSE WAS SO BIG AND EMPTY.
AND SO OFTEN, SEIJI AND I WERE
THE ONLY ONES THERE.
MY PARENTS FREQUENTLY SENT ME TO
MY UNCLE’S PLACE, EVEN BEFORE MY
BROTHER WAS BORN.
I LOVED HAVING FREE REIGN OF HIS
STUDY.
AND THAT’S WHERE I FOUND IT.
I’D BEEN TOLD THAT IT WAS
SMUGGLED IN FROM SOME FOREIGN
COUNTRY.
MY UNCLE SEEMED POSSESSED BY IT.
SOMETIMES HE WOULD EVEN SPEAK TO
IT.
IT WAS INDEED BEAUTIFUL.
FAR MORE THAN ANY DOLL MY UNCLE
HAD GIVEN ME.
ODDLY ENOUGH, THERE WAS NO SENSE
OF BRUTALITY TO IT.
AS IF THE HEAD WAS COMPLETE,
JUST AS IT WAS.
BUT IT WAS NEVER ANYTHING MORE
TO ME.
THAT’S WHY I DIDN’T THINK TWICE
ABOUT ALLOWING SEIJI INTO THE
STUDY THAT DAY.
IT WAS HARMLESS, JUST PART OF
OUR USUAL PLAY.
OR MAYBE, I JUST WANTED TO SHARE
THE SECRET.
SEE? PRETTY, ISN’T IT?
>> [gasps]
>> [awed sigh]
>> [scoffs]
AND THAT’S HOW IT ALL BEGAN.
A THOUGHTLESS ACTION, WHICH
BECAME THE SINGLE BIGGEST REGRET
OF MY WHOLE LIFE.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST TIME WE’VE
MET, CORRECT?
I HOPE THAT LIST OF ILLEGAL
ALIENS WAS USEFUL,
MS. NAMIE YAGIRI.
I’M GLAD TO SEE YOU.
YOU’RE THE SIXTH CHIEF OF
YAGIRI PHARMACEUTICALS.
IT’S AN HONOR TO HAVE YOU COME
AND VISIT MY HUMBLE ABODE.
SO PLEASE, HAVE A SEAT,
MS. YAGIRI.
>> I NEED YOU TO FIND MY
BROTHER.
IT’S URGENT.
>> HUH?
>> I’M WILLING TO PAY YOU
HOWEVER MUCH YOU ASK.
I HAVEN’T HEARD A WORD FROM HIM
SINCE LAST NIGHT.
BUT HE SHOULD STILL BE IN
IKEBUKURO.
>> HE REALLY HASN’T BEEN OUT OF
CONTACT ALL THAT LONG.
WHAT HAS YOU SO WORRIED ABOUT
HIM?
>> IT’S THE GIRL THAT HE’S WITH.
SHE HAS A DISTINCTIVE SCAR
AROUND HER NECK.
>> A GIRL?
[laughs]
HE IS A BOY WITH NEEDS.
>> GET STARTED AT ONCE!
>> WHOA, WHOA, WAIT A SEC.
DON’T YOU THINK THAT THERE ARE
FAR MORE IMPORTANT THINGS THAT
WE SHOULD BE LOOKING INTO FIRST?
RUMOR HAS IT THE FOREIGN ENTITY
NEBRA HAS BEEN MAKING SERIOUS
ADVANCES TOWARDS ACQUIRING YOUR
COMPANY.
NOW THAT WOULD MAKE YOUR CURRENT
POSITION--
>> MR. IZAYA ORIHARA, I DON’T
HAVE TIME TO CHITCHAT RIGHT
NOW.
>> HMM. SURPRISING.
A WOMAN LIKE YOU, FALLING FOR
HER BROTHER.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT?
>> YOU DON’T KNOW A SINGLE THING
ABOUT ME.
>> I KNOW THE NAME NAMIE YAGIRI,
AND ALL SHE’S ACHIEVED.
YOUR UNCLE TOOK SOME BIG RISKS
THAT DIDN’T TURN OUT SO WELL,
LOST THE FAMILY BUSINESS, AND
NOW THE CURRENT PRESIDENT OF
YAGIRI PHARMACEUTICALS IS A VERY
BUTTONED-DOWN, PRACTICAL MAN.
BUT YOU CAME INTO THE COMPANY ON
THE BOTTOM FLOOR AND, LIKE THE
SMART GIRL YOU ARE, WORKED YOUR
WAY UP THE LADDER.
YOU’VE GOT BRAINS AND BEAUTY.
>> I GUESS YOU DO KNOW ME FAIRLY
WELL.
A GUY LIKE YOU SHOULD HAVE NO
PROBLEM FINDING MY BROTHER.
>> RIGHT, THE BROTHER.
MAYBE THIS IS ONE AFFAIR YOU
SHOULDN’T MEDDLE IN.
>> WHAT I’M DOING IS NOT
MEDDLING.
THE ONLY ONE CAPABLE OF
PROTECTING HIM IS ME!
>> IT’S ALWAYS SO HARD TO SEE
THE OBVIOUS WHEN YOU’RE STALKING
SOMEONE.
THE STALKER THINKS THEY’RE
PROTECTING THEIR VICT--
>> DON’T YOU EVER COMPARE ME TO
A STALKER AGAIN!
>> SCARY.
I WAS ONLY KIDDING.
OKAY, I’LL HELP.
BUT IN THE WAY I SEE FIT.
WE INFORMANTS WORK DIFFERENTLY
THAN COPS.
[typing]
>> JUST WHAT KIND OF GAME IS
THAT?
>> QUESTION.
THE GIRL YOU MENTIONED WITH THE
SCAR ON HER NECK.
ARE YOU JEALOUS OF HER?
>> WHY DO YOU ASK?
>> MM-HMM.
[laughs]
[types]
>> I CAN’T POSSIBLY BE JEALOUS
OF HER.
MY HEART BURNS WITH JEALOUSY,
BUT ONLY BECAUSE--
>> SISTER, THERE’S A GIRL THAT I
REALLY LIKE.
>> I COULD SEE THAT SEIJI WAS
GROWING ODDER AND ODDER BY THE
DAY.
HE KEPT TRYING TO SNEAK INTO MY
UNCLE’S STUDY, AND ONCE HE WAS
IN, HE WOULD STARE AT IT FOR
HOURS.
WHAT HE LOVED WAS NOT A PERSON.
IT HAD NO HEART, NOT EVEN A
BODY.
[sighs]
I FELT I HAD TO GET IT AWAY FROM
HIM.
SO AS SOON AS I JOINED THE
COMPANY, I ASKED MY UNCLE TO
RELOCATE IT THERE FOR RESEARCH
PURPOSES.
AND THEN IT HAPPENED.
NEBRA HAD BEGUN TALKS WITH OUR
BOARD, AND I WAS TRYING TO
PROTECT OUR CLASSIFIED RESEARCH
FROM LEAKS.
BUT THEN A SECURITY CARD WAS
STOLEN.
IT WAS A CARD THAT ONLY I HAD
ACCESS TO.
[beeps]
[gasps]
>> SIS.
I THINK THAT I MIGHT HAVE KILLED
SOMEONE.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
>> UPON HEARING THOSE WORDS, THE
FEELING IN MY CHEST WAS NEITHER
FEAR NOR ANGER.
INSTEAD, IT WAS PURE HAPPINESS.
SEIJI NEEDED HELP, AND HE CALLED
ME.
>> [sighs]
>> [slurping]
>> JUST TRY TO RELAX.
YOU DON’T NEED TO WORRY ABOUT A
THING.
YOUR BIG SIS WILL HANDLE IT ALL.
OKAY?
>> I’VE GOT A QUESTION.
BUT NOT ABOUT THAT GIRL.
>> SO I’M GUESSING THAT YOU WERE
THE ONE WHO TOOK IT, THEN.
IT’LL ALL WORK OUT.
JUST GIVE HER BACK TO ME, AND
I’LL FIX EVERYTHING.
IT’S GONNA BE FINE, I PROMISE.
>> [slurping]
>> I HAD NO IDEA AT THE TIME
THAT SEIJI WAS BEING HOUNDED BY
SOME STUPID LITTLE GIRL NAMED
MIKA HARIMA, OR THAT SHE WAS
STALKING HIM.
SHE HAD SNUCK INTO HIS ROOM, AND
THAT’S WHEN SHE SAW IT.
I’LL GO TO WHATEVER LENGTHS I
HAVE TO TO PROTECT YOU.
>> AH, HERE WE GO.
SEEMS FINDING HIM WON’T BE A
PROBLEM AT ALL.
THE COPS HAVE HIM IN THEIR
POSSESSION AS WE SPEAK.
I’M SURE THEY’LL BE CALLING YOU
SOON.
>> [gasps]
>> DON’T WORRY ABOUT THE POLICE
PART.
I’M SURE THAT IT’S PROBABLY
NOTHING.
PROBABLY.
>> I’VE HAD ENOUGH FROM YOU!
[phone rings]
HELLO?
YES, SPEAKING.
>> [chuckles]
>> [gasping]
>> HEY, WHAT’S WRONG?
WHAT, WE’RE LEAVING?
BUT WE HAVEN’T--
HEY, WAIT.
IT MAKES ME SO HAPPY THAT YOU
LOVE ME AS MUCH AS YOU DO.
AND I WILL ALWAYS LOVE YOU.
I MEAN IT.
FOREVER.
>> I’M SCARED.
>> SCARED OF WHAT?
>> LET’S LEAVE THIS PLACE.
LET’S GO FAR AWAY.
>> LISTEN, I WANT TO GO WHEREVER
YOU WANT TO GO.
BUT TELL ME WHERE THAT IS.
>> HMM? WHAT THE HELL?
>> [straining]
>> A LOVER’S SPAT?
>> [panting]
>> [surprised gasp]
>> [gasping and panting]
[frightened gasp]
NO!
STOP! GO AWAY!
[panicked screams]
>> ALL RIGHT, STOP WITH THE
HYSTERICS.
RELAX, WE’RE NOT HERE TO HURT
YOU.
CALM DOWN.
>> [screaming]
>> DID YOU HEAR WHAT I JUST
SAID?
[grunting]
HUH?
>> [screaming]
[techno feedback]
♪ ♪
>> HUH?
>> YOU LET GO OF HER RIGHT NOW!
>> [gasping]
>> GO ON, DON’T WORRY ABOUT ME.
THIS DOESN’T HURT.
GO.
I DON’T KNOW WHAT THIS IS ALL
ABOUT.
BUT YOU DO WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
HEH.
I’VE ALWAYS WANTED TO SAY THIS.
GO ON AHEAD AND LEAVE THIS ONE
TO ME, GOT IT?
>> WAIT!
[crowd murmuring]
>> [gasps]
[horse neighs]
[techno rock]
♪ ♪
>> [groaning]
>> I’M SO SORRY.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU’RE THAT--
AAH!
[crowd gasping]
>> GET YOUR HANDS OFF HER NOW!
>> EASY, PAL.
YOU’RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
>> [groans]
LET ME GO!
>> TELL ME, IS THAT YOUR
GIRLFRIEND?
>> SHE IS.
FATE BROUGHT US TOGETHER.
>> SO THEN, WHY IS SHE ACTING
LIKE THAT?
>> BEATS ME.
>> WHAT THE HELL KIND OF ANSWER
IS THAT?
>> [yelling]
[groans]
>> SO YOU SAY THAT YOU LOVE HER,
BUT YOU DON’T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT HER.
GUESS YOU’RE A PRETTY LAME
BOYFRIEND, THEN, AREN’T YOU?
>> ALL THAT I NEED TO KNOW ABOUT
HER IS THAT I LOVE HER.
THAT’S ALL.
>> OKAY.
THEN EDUCATE ME.
HOW DID FATE BRING YOU BOTH
TOGETHER?
>> IT’S BECAUSE I LOVE HER.
IT’S JUST AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
LOVE IS A FEELING.
YOU CAN’T EXPLAIN IT.
IT HAS NO WORDS!
>> [grunts]
>> NOW LET ME GO.
[horse neighs]
[crowd screaming]
[girls shrieking]
>> both: THE BLACK RIDER!
>> MY ACTIONS WILL PROVE MY
LOVE!
JUST WATCH.
I’LL PROVE IT.
>> [grunts]
[growls]
I LIKE YOU A LOT BETTER THAN
IZAYA.
SO I’M ONLY GOING TO SEND YOU
HOME WITH THIS.
[smack]
[groans]
THIS’LL JUST BLEED IF I TAKE IT
OUT.
BETTER STOP AND GET A BAND-AID.
OR MAYBE SOME SUPERGLUE WILL DO
THE TRICK.
[siren wailing]
>> SO WHAT YOU’RE SAYING IS YOUR
HEAD WALKED BY ATTACHED TO
ANOTHER BODY?
YOU GRABBED HER, BUT SOME HIGH
SCHOOL KID INTERCEPTED.
YOU CHASED HER, BUT THEN SOME
OTHER HIGH SCHOOL KID ENTERED
THE SCENE.
AND THAT’S WHEN THE TWO OF THEM
ESCAPED WITH YOUR HEAD.
AND THAT’S WHAT YOU EXPECT ME TO
BELIEVE?
>> BELIEVE IT IF YOU WANT.
IT’S YOUR CHOICE.
>> NO, I BELIEVE IT.
BUT WHAT WAS SHIZUO DOING THERE?
>> OH, I FORGOT THAT PART.
IZAYA HAD ASKED ME TO BE IN THE
PARK ON STANDBY FOR A JOB.
SHIZUO PASSED BY, SO WE JUST
STARTED TO TALK.
BUT THEN I GOT A TEXT A FEW
MINUTES LATER THAT HE DIDN’T
NEED ME, AND I WAS JUST GETTING
READY TO COME BACK HERE.
>> HMM.
IZAYA CALLED YOU.
HUH.
>> REGARDLESS, I WANTED TO TALK
TO YOU.
>> YOU’RE STILL SHAKEN UP,
AREN’T YOU?
YOU CAN TALK TO ME AS MUCH AS
YOU LIKE.
>> WHY IS SOME OTHER BODY
WALKING AROUND WITH MY HEAD ON
ITS SHOULDERS?
>> RELAX.
I’M NOT GOING TO HAVE A
CLEAR-CUT ANSWER FOR THIS, BUT
IF I HAD TO TAKE A GUESS, I
WOULD PROBABLY SAY SOMETHING
LIKE, YOUR HEAD WAS LOOKING FOR
ANOTHER HOST THAT WOULD BE
APPROPRIATE, AND WHEN IT FOUND
ONE IT LIKED, IT ATTACHED TO IT.
>> THAT’S HORRIBLE!
>> MAYBE YOUR HEAD STUMBLED
ACROSS A FRESH CORPSE.
>> OKAY, ENOUGH.
[sighs]
I DON’T KNOW.
MAYBE WHAT YOU’RE SUGGESTING IS
POSSIBLE.
>> WHAT I DID WASN’T WRONG.
IT WAS DONE FOR ALL THE RIGHT
REASONS.
THE EXPERIMENT WE PERFORMED,
THAT WAS ALL DONE FOR SEIJI’S
SAKE.
>> I HAVE TO GO.
>> IT’S FINE.
EVERYTHING’S ALL RIGHT NOW.
>> I HAVE TO GO.
>> YOU MUST HAVE BEEN SO SCARED.
>> BUT AS YOU CAN SEE, NOTHING
HAPPENED TO YOU.
EVEN AFTER SHE ESCAPED FROM HERE
AND FOUND SEIJI AGAIN, MY LOVE
FOR HIM NEVER WAIVERED.
NOT ONCE.
IT IS ONLY BECAUSE OF MY LOVE
FOR SEIJI THAT HE HAS ANY LOVE
FOR THAT GIRL.
SEIJI KNOWS THIS TO BE TRUE, AND
SO DO I.
EVERYTHING MAY HAVE GOTTEN A BIT
TWISTED, BUT IT WILL STILL WORK
OUT.
>> DAMN IT.
HE WAS WEARING A RAIRA UNIFORM.
SO THEN, WHO IS HE?
>> JUST LEAVE IT TO ME.
I’LL FIND HIM.
>> WHAT I HAVE TO DO NOW IS FIND
THAT KID FROM RAIRA.
THEN I NEED TO BE ABLE TO TALK
TO MY HEAD.
>> DO YOU MEAN THE HEAD THAT
SHRIEKED WHEN IT FIRST SAW YOU?
HOW DO YOU INTEND TO GET YOUR
HEAD BACK ANYWAY?
IT’S ATTACHED TO ANOTHER BODY.
WHAT’S YOUR PLAN?
DO YOU THINK SHE’LL JUST SNAP
OFF HER HEAD AND GIVE IT TO YOU?
>> [sighs]
>> CELTY...
>> I JUST DON’T WANT TO ACCEPT
THAT MY HEAD AND MY MEMORIES ARE
GONE FOR GOOD.
THAT MEANS EVERYTHING I’VE DONE
FOR THE PAST 20 YEARS HAS BEEN
A COMPLETE WASTE OF TIME.
>> IT WASN’T A WASTE OF TIME.
>> ALL RIGHT, I’M GOING TO GO
GET HER NOW AND BRING HER BACK
FOR YOU.
YOU JUST STAY HERE UNTIL I
RETURN.
BY THE WAY.
YOUR CELL PHONE--WHERE IS IT?
>> I DON’T KNOW.
I REMEMBER PUTTING IT IN MY BAG,
BUT IT’S GONE NOW.
>> HUH?
>> SHE NEEDS ME.
I HAVE TO FIND HER!
WE ARE MEANT TO BE TOGETHER.
>> AH...I HEAR YOU.
DON’T WORRY, NOW.
YOU JUST LEAVE EVERYTHING TO ME.
[sighs]
THAT GIRL’S GOT NERVE.
A DOLL SHOULD BEHAVE LIKE A DOLL
AND STAY PUT.
THE LAST THING IT SHOULD DO IS
INTERFERE WITH MY LOVE FOR
SEIJI.
I’VE MADE UP MY MIND.
I DON’T WANT ANY MORE REGRETS.
I’M THROUGH WITH THAT.
OKAY, LISTEN.
I WANT YOU TO ROUND UP EVERY
PERSON WE HAVE FOR THIS.
I WANT HER DEAD OR ALIVE.
IF YOU HAVE ANY TROUBLE BRINGING
HER BACK, THEN DISPOSE OF HER.
>> [sighs]
>> [laughs]
I SEE.
EVERYONE IS BUSY.
THIS’LL BE FUN.
THIS’LL BE FUN, THIS’LL BE FUN.
THERE’S JUST SO MUCH GOING ON IN
THIS TOWN THAT EVEN I DON’T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT.
IT’S AN ENDLESS SEA OF
ENTERTAINMENT.
THIS IS WHY I LOVE THIS BUSTLING
HOTBED OF HUMANS.
I LOVE THEM.
I LOVE THEM ALL.
I LOVE THEM ALL SO MUCH!
AND THAT IS WHY MY LOVELY LITTLE
HUMANS SHOULD LOVE AND ADORE ME
TOO.
>> THANKS A LOT.
>> ARE YOU OKAY NOW?
CAN YOU ANSWER MY QUESTIONS?
>> MM...
>> YOU SAID YOU DON’T REMEMBER
ANYTHING.
SO THEN, DO YOU THINK MAYBE YOU
HAVE AMNESIA?
WELL, I’M GONNA SUGGEST IT
AGAIN.
I THINK WE SHOULD GO TO THE
POLICE, OR TO A HOSPITAL.
>> MM. I’M SORRY.
SORRY.
I’M SORRY!
>> IT’S OKAY, NO BIG DEAL.
>> I’M SORRY.
>> DON’T APOLOGIZE.
>> I HAVE TO GO.
BEFORE THAT WOMAN GETS IN MY
WAY.
>> FOREVER AND EVER.
>> I HAVE TO GO.
>> SEIJI.
>> both: I LOVE YOU.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> SO THE HEADLESS RIDER, IZAYA
ORIHARA, AND THAT GIRL WITH THE
SCAR, THEY ALL SHOWED UP AGAIN.
AND THEN THAT GUY IN THE OTHER
CLASS IS IN THE DOLLARS.
NEXT TIME, NEVER BEFORE SEEN.
I REALLY WANTED AN UNUSUAL LIFE,
BUT...