[Complication
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK’D]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> YOU ARE NOTHING BUT A
DISGUSTING LEECH.
WHAT AN EASY TIME YOU HAVE.
>> I JUST WANT TO GET STRONGER
SO THAT SOMEDAY I CAN CONTAIN MY
ANGER.
>> MY LOVE, MY LOVE, MY LOVE,
MY LOVE, MY LOVE!
>> SAIKA’S DESIRE IS ULTIMATELY
TO LOVE PEOPLE.
>> WE’RE SO LOOKING FORWARD TO
LOVING YOU.
>> NOW I CAN FINALLY GO ALL OUT.
RAAH!
>> BUT I MUST RELY ON SAIKA TO
LOVE OTHER PEOPLE FOR ME.
I TRULY AM HER PARASITE.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> [laughs]
>> OKAY, ANRI, WE’RE GONNA GO
HIGHER!
>> THIS...IS A LIE.
>> LOOK AT YOU, ANRI.
>> THIS...IS THE TRUTH.
>> [gasps]
>> [sobs]
[people muttering]
[screaming]
>> [babbling]
[grunting]
>> HE’S STRONG...
NO. HE’S SCARY.
ACTUALLY, HE’S AWESOME!
[mumbling]
>> [grunts and strains]
[shouts]
[screaming]
>> AMAZING.
I KNEW HE WAS STRONG...
BUT I HAD NO IDEA HE WAS THIS
STRONG.
[grunting and screaming]
>> [gasps]
>> HUH?
YOU THINK SOMETHIN’ HAPPENED?
WHY DON’T YOU GO CHECK IT OUT.
AFTER ALL, YOU’RE NOT DOIN’
ANYTHING ELSE RIGHT NOW.
>> THEY’RE MADE FROM THE SAME
STUFF MY SCYTHE IS.
SOMETHING LIKE A BLADE WON’T
CUT THROUGH THEM.
>> THANKS, PERFECT.
ALL RIGHTY THEN...
>> NO WAY.
THAT SWORD CAN’T BE SAIKA.
BUT THEN THAT MEANS...
THE BLADE THAT ATTACKED ME THAT
NIGHT...
SO YOU--YOU KILLED YOUR OWN
PARENTS.
[gasps]
>> YOUR BLADE IS ONE OF SAIKA’S
CHILDREN.
BUT I GUESS IT DIDN’T TEACH
YOU HOW TO FIGHT.
PLEASE, TALK TO THE OTHER
CHILDREN, TELL THEM TO STOP.
YOU’RE THE PARENT OF THOSE
BLADES.
IF YOU ORDER THEM TO DO
SOMETHING, THEY’LL DO IT.
IF YOU’RE NOT GOING TO DO THIS,
YOU’LL LEAVE ME NO CHOICE.
MY SWORD’S THE ORIGINAL SAIKA,
THE PARENT OF YOUR BLADE...
AND IF I CHOOSE, IT CAN COMMAND
YOUR BLADE AND--
>> I DON’T BELIEVE YOU!
I’M THE ONE THAT CAN CONTROL
SAIKA. AND I DO IT THROUGH
LOVE, AN EMOTION YOU KNOW
NOTHING ABOUT!
>> I WANT YOU TO HEAR THIS, JUST
FOR A SECOND.
I WANT YOU TO HEAR...
THE WORDS THAT ECHO INSIDE
ME.
THEY’RE WORDS OF LOVE...
FROM SAIKA.
>> [exclaims]
>> I LOVE YOU.
I CARE SO MUCH.
I ONLY WANT TO BE WITH YOU.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
[voices overlapping and echoing]
>> DON’T KNOW WHAT YOU’RE
SAYING.
>> CAN’T YOU SEE THAT?
>> WHY DON’T YOU LISTEN TO ME?
>> [whimpers]
[cries out]
>> THAT WAS THE LIE.
[laughter]
THIS WAS THE TRUTH.
>> STOP!
PLEASE STOP!
>> HER FATHER WAS AN
ANTIQUITIES DEALER.
AND WHEN HIS BUSINESS BEGAN TO
FAIL, HE TOOK THAT RAGE OUT
ON HIS FAMILY.
GRADUALLY, SHE SEALED UP HER
HEART AND WITHDREW INTO HERSELF.
AND THAT’S WHEN THE SLASHER
APPEARED.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
[slashing sound and shout]
>> [echoing] I LOVE YOU, I LOVE
YOU, I LOVE YOU...
I LOVE YOU, HONEY.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
[slashing sound]
[thud]
>> THAT SLASHER...
WAS HER MOTHER.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I KNOW YOU DO.
>> YOU MEAN SO MUCH TO ME.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW MUCH I
CARE.
>> I AM SO PROUD OF YOU.
YOU WILL ALWAYS BE IMPORTANT TO
ME.
>> I LOVE YOU.
[echoing "I love you"s]
>> [yells]
[screaming]
[yells]
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
WE CARVED OUR LOVE INTO HIM.
WHY HASN’T HE CHANGED?
>> ONCE HE’S BEEN CUT, HE’LL
OPEN UP TO US.
OUR MINDS WILL FLOW INTO HIM...
INTO HIS PAIN AND FEAR.
IT’S JUST A MATTER OF TIME NOW.
>> SHIZUO HEIWAJIMA FEELS NO
FEAR?
>> OW!
>> COME ON! COME ON! COME ON!
COME ON! COME ON! COME ON!
[yells]
[screaming]
LOOK, YOU BASTARDS GOT IT
ALL WRONG.
YOU GUYS THINK THAT NO ONE’LL
EVER LOVE ME ’CAUSE THEY’LL
ALWAYS BE SCARED OF ME.
THAT’S RIDICULOUS.
YOU SEE THE ONE WHO’S SCARED
IS ME.
I’M ALWAYS AFRAID THAT I’LL
LOSE CONTROL AND THEN SCREW
EVERYTHING UP.
I’M THE BIGGEST COWARD I’VE
EVER MET.
BUT HEY, WHO GIVES A DAMN?
IN THE END, THAT’S GOT NOTHIN’
TO DO WITH ME KICKIN’ YOUR ASS.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE’S NO WAY THAT I’M GOIN’
DOWN IN FRONT OF THE PEOPLE
WHO LOVE ME.
>> I LOVE YOU!
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> all: I LOVE YOU.
>> [gasps]
[whimpers]
TELL ME...
HOW CAN YOU STAND THAT VOICE?
>> THERE ARE SEVERAL QUALITIES
THAT I LACK AS A PERSON.
AND SO TO COMPENSATE FOR THAT
I LEECH OFF PEOPLE WHO POSSESS
THE THINGS I DON’T, LIKE A
PARASITE.
YOU SEE, MY HEART ISN’T
CAPABLE OF LOVING OTHER PEOPLE.
SO I CAN BEAR THIS VOICE
INSIDE ME FOREVER, OBJECTIVELY
AND FAIRLY.
>> [screams]
>> [whimpers]
>> [laughs]
I DID IT!
I CAN’T BELIEVE YOU THOUGHT YOU
COULD BEAT ME.
>> WHAT’S WRONG?
WHY ARE YOU SCARED?
YOU SAID CUTTING SOMEONE’S A
SIGN OF LOVE.
>> YOU STOOD THERE AND LET ME
CUT YOU!
HOW COME?
>> BECAUSE I’M ABOUT TO DO
SOMETHING AWFUL TO YOU.
BUT NOW AT LEAST WE’RE EVEN.
WHAT I’M ABOUT TO DO IS ALLOW
MY SAIKA TO CONTROL YOUR MIND.
I WON’T APOLOGIZE.
IF I DID, IT WOULD INVALIDATE
EVERYTHING I’VE DONE MY ENTIRE
LIFE.
I KNOW THIS MAY SEEM A BIT
DEVIOUS.
BUT I WILL HAVE PEACE IN MY
LIFE, EVEN IF I MUST USE YOU
IN A HORRIBLE WAY TO GET IT.
YOU SEE, I HAVE NO OTHER CHOICE.
I TRULY AM A PARASITE.
>> [gasps]
>> I LOVE YOU! I LOVE YOU!
>> SAIKA IS SUCH A LONELY
CREATURE.
I KNOW FROM OUR PERSPECTIVE
WHAT SHE’S DOING MAY SEEM WRONG.
BUT SHE DOES GENUINELY LOVE
HUMANS.
SO NOW IT’S YOUR TURN...
IT’S TIME FOR YOU TO LOVE SAIKA
TOO.
UNLIKE ME, YOU HAVE THE ABILITY
TO LOVE OTHER PEOPLE.
>> [roars]
STOP!
COME ON, STOP, DAMN IT!
>> [whimpers]
>> WHAT?
>> WHERE ARE WE?
>> WHAT’S GOING ON?
>> THIS IS REALLY CREEPY.
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
>> NO ONE ENDED UP DYING, HUH?
[laughs]
>> HUH?
>> WELL, BODY...
I WAS FINALLY ABLE TO CONTROL
YOU.
>> ANRI, IS THAT REALLY YOU?
>> HUH?
>> THAT ISN’T THE FIRST TIME
THAT GIRL’S COME AFTER ME WITH A
KNIFE.
LAST TIME I JUST PLAYED IT DOWN
AND HAD HER TRANSFERRED.
I GUESS SHE STILL HADN’T--
[ghost horse neighing]
ANRI, WE NEED TO GET OUT OF
HERE.
LOOK, ANRI, I’VE DONE A WHOLE
LOT TO TRY AND HELP YOU OUT.
DID YOU FORGET?
WHO DO YOU THINK MADE IT
POSSIBLE FOR YOU AND MIKA TO GET
IN THE SAME CLASS?
>> AND THAT DEBT HAS ALREADY
BEEN REPAID.
>> HOW DO YOU MEAN?
REPAID HOW?
>> AT FIRST, I THOUGHT THE BLACK
RIDER WAS THE SLASHER.
AND FOR A WHILE, I THOUGHT YOU
MIGHT BE ATTACKED NEXT.
I WANTED TO HELP.
SO I TRIED MY BEST TO PROTECT
YOU.
I WASN’T DOING IT BECAUSE I
LIKE YOU.
I WAS SIMPLY DOING IT BECAUSE I
DIDN’T WANT TO OWE YOU ANYTHING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> I KNOW THE BLACK RIDER WAS
CHASING YOU, BUT I DON’T KNOW
WHAT FOR.
WHAT DID YOU DO TO PROVOKE HER?
>> HE’S THE GUY FROM THAT NIGHT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO...
ANRI! OKAY...
THERE’S NO NEED TO HURT ANYONE.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO, HUH?
CUT ME LIKE HARUNA DID?
PUT THAT BLADE DOWN!
>> NO.
I COULDN’T BE LIKE HARUNA IF
I TRIED.
YOU SEE, WHILE HARUNA LIKED
YOU, I DETEST YOU.
>> [screams]
[upbeat Japanese music]
>> SHE’S FLAT-CHESTED AND
PREPUBESCENT!
[giggles]
HEY, BY THE WAY, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT DENGEKI BUNKO’S PUTTIN’
OUT THIS MONTH?
>> NO MORE BAD BEHAVIOR IN
THIS VAN, IT’LL STICK OUT
ANYWHERE.
>> HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT, I
WONDER IF KINO’S JOURNEY IS
EVER GONNA ADD ANOTHER CHAPTER
TO IT.
>> YEAH, AND CALL IT SOMETHING
LIKE SHIZU’S JOURNEY!
>> EVEN BETTER, "SAMOEDO KAMEN
SHOULDN’T BE THIS CUTE!"
>> SHOULD’VE KNOWN BETTER THAN
TO LET WALKER HANDLE REPLACING
THE DOOR, MAN.
DAMN IT.
>> SABURO, WHY’S YOUR FACE SO
RED?
>> YOU GOT A FEVER OR SOMETHING?
>> SHUT UP!
>> ANRI, ARE YOU SURE YOU’RE
OKAY?
>> YEAH, IT REALLY ISN’T THAT
BAD.
>> WHEN MASAOMI TOLD ME WHAT
HAPPENED, I WAS SHOCKED.
I CAN’T BELIEVE YOU WERE HURT.
SO WHERE IS MASAOMI ANYWAY?
>> HE LEFT A LITTLE BIT AGO.
SAID HE HAD SOMETHING TO TAKE
CARE OF.
>> MAN, WHAT COULD BE SO
IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW?
>> I’M FINE.
HE DIDN’T NEED TO STAY.
>> SO HAVE YOU TALKED TO THE
POLICE YET?
FROM WHAT I HEARD, THERE WERE A
WHOLE LOT OF PEOPLE WHO ENDED
UP GETTING HURT AND...
>> NO, IT’S OKAY.
>> IT’S NOT OKAY!
>> I THINK THE ATTACKS ARE OVER
NOW.
I JUST HAVE THAT FEELING.
>> AND WHY’S THAT?
>> [laughs]
OH, I SHOULDN’T LAUGH.
THE TRUTH IS, SEVERAL HOURS
BEFORE I GOT HURT, I HAD
ANOTHER RUN-IN WITH THE
SLASHER TOO.
IT’S KINDA CRAZY, BUT I WAS
SAVED BY ALL THESE PEOPLE.
AND SOME OF THEM WERE JUST SO
SUPER COOL.
>> SO...SO SUPER COOL?
WHAT’S GOIN’ ON?
>> THERE WAS THIS BARTENDER
GUY WITH SUNGLASSES...
>> WHAT?
IS SHE TALKING ABOUT SHIZUO?
>> AND THERE WAS THIS OTHER
REALLY AWESOME PERSON.
YOU WON’T BELIEVE IT WHEN I
TELL YOU...
I MET THE HEADLESS RIDER!
>> WH--SO...
WAIT A SECOND!
>> I GOT TO TALK TO IT FOR A FEW
MINUTES.
IT WAS SO AMAZING.
YOU COULD TELL IT REALLY CARED
ABOUT PEOPLE.
IT IS ODD.
YOU PROBABLY DON’T BELIEVE ME,
DO YOU?
>> NO, I MEAN, IF YOU’RE SAYING
IT’S TRUE...
BUT CELTY’S A WOMAN!
>> AND THEN WHEN I WAS ATTACKED
A SECOND TIME, THE HEADLESS
RIDER APPEARED OUT OF NOWHERE
AND SAVED ME AGAIN.
I GUESS THAT’S WHY I FEEL LIKE
I’LL BE OKAY.
>> YEAH, BUT THE HEADLESS RIDER
IS...
>> HUH?
>> I CAN’T TELL HER, BECAUSE
IF I DO...
WELL, YOU SEE, IT’S JUST THAT
THOSE PEOPLE, THE WORLD THOSE
GUYS LIVE IN IS JUST SO
ENTIRELY DIFFERENT FROM OURS...
YOU MIGHT WANT TO KEEP YOUR
DISTANCE FROM THEM.
>> TELL ME, MIKADO, WHAT DO
YOU THINK A TRULY UNUSUAL LIFE
WOULD BE LIKE?
SOMETHING REALLY UNIQUE.
>> HUH?
>> IT’D BE THE KIND OF LIFE
WHERE, EVERY SINGLE DAY,
NOTHING NEW EVER HAPPENED.
NOTHING CHANGED.
THAT KIND OF A LIFE IS TRULY
UNUSUAL.
>> I’LL HAVE A DOCTOR I KNOW
TAKE A LOOK AT HER.
DON’T WORRY.
>> CELTY, I--LISTEN, I REALLY...
>> DON’T APOLOGIZE.
YOU DID WHAT YOU THOUGHT WAS
BEST, DIDN’T YOU?
AND IF IT MAKES YOU FEEL
BETTER, I THINK IT WAS RIGHT
TOO.
I DO THINK KNOCKING MY HEAD OFF
TOOK THINGS A BIT TOO FAR, BUT
I’LL TAKE THAT UP WITH SAIKA.
I’M NOT ENDORSING EVERYTHING
YOU DID.
I JUST THINK IF WE WERE TO
FIGHT, YOU’D WIN.
IF YOU STILL HAVE YOUR DOUBTS,
THEN I SUGGEST YOU STOP
QUESTIONING YOURSELF AND
INSTEAD USE THAT POWER YOU HAVE
TO BETTER THIS TOWN.
>> SHE HAD OBTAINED A POWER.
A POWER THAT ALLOWED HER TO
CONTROL A HUNDRED SAIKAS AND
BEND THEM TO HER WILL.
IT WAS NO SMALL BURDEN FOR
HER TO BEAR.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, IT
WAS A LOAD SHE WAS GLAD TO
CARRY.
SHE’D ALWAYS FELT SOMEWHAT
ADRIFT BEFORE.
BUT NOW, WITH THE FATE OF
OTHERS WEIGHING IN HER HANDS,
SHE FINALLY FELT GROUNDED IN
REALITY.
[buzzing sound]
>> [gasps]
>> JUST THEN, SHE HEARD A
VOICE.
IT SAID, "I MAY NOT LOVE YOU,
BUT I DON’T HATE YOU."
PERHAPS IT WAS JUST HER
IMAGINATION.
SO SHE CALLED OUT TO THE
VOICE, BUT NO ONE ANSWERED.
WHICH, IN THE END, WAS FINE BY
HER.
ACTUALLY, IT MADE HER A
LITTLE HAPPY.
>> [gasps]
>> IT SEEMED THAT FINALLY HER
LIFE HAD GONE BACK TO NORMAL.
HOWEVER, SHE COULDN’T TELL
THEM THE TRUTH.
NOT ABOUT SAIKA OR THE
PERSON PULLING THE STRINGS.
WHEN SHE TOOK CONTROL OF
ALL THE SAIKAS, SHE ABSORBED
THE MEMORIES HARUNA NIEKAWA
HAD WITH THOSE BLADES.
THAT’S HOW SHE DISCOVERED WHO
WAS BEHIND THIS.
SHE DIDN’T KNOW WHAT HE WAS
AFTER.
BUT IF THAT PERSON HURT
MIKADO OR MASAOMI OR DISTURBED
THEIR PEACE, SHE KNEW SHE’D
HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
RELIVING IT AGAIN WAS
HORRIBLE, BUT SHE WAS
DETERMINED TO REMEMBER HIS
NAME.
THEN IT CAME TO HER.
>> IZAYA ORIHARA IS STRANGE.
I CAN’T BELIEVE YOUR PARENTS
NAMED YOU THAT.
>> IT MAY BE A COINCIDENCE THAT
I’VE TURNED OUT THE WAY THAT I
HAVE.
BUT THE NAME DOES FIT ME
PERFECTLY.
DO YOU BELIEVE IN COINCIDENCE,
NAMIE?
>> WHY DO YOU ASK?
>> I THINK MOST PEOPLE WILL
ATTRIBUTE THESE RECENT EVENTS
TO NOTHING MORE THAN
COINCIDENCE.
BUT YOU SEE, I SENT NASUJIMA TO
THE GIRL’S HOUSE AT THAT HOUR
OF THE NIGHT.
THAT POOR SUCKER WAS TRULY AN
IDIOT.
HE COULD HAVE FOUND
ANRI SONOHARA’S ADDRESS JUST BY
PEEKING AT HIS CLASS ROSTER.
YOU SEE, ONCE YOU ACCEPT THEY
EXIST, THE HARD PART IS OVER.
THEY’RE SUDDENLY EVERYWHERE.
DEMONIC BLADES, FAERIES,
THERE’S NO END.
>> HMM?
>> ACTUALLY, THE ONLY REAL
COINCIDENCE, WAS WHEN
NASUJIMA RAN OFF WITH MY CASH.
HE OWED SOME SERIOUS DEBTS.
SO HE TRIED TO GET THE CASH BY
THREATENING THE PARENTS OF
HARUNA NIEKAWA, THE GIRL WHO’D
BEEN STALKING HIM AT SCHOOL.
THE LOAN SHARKS HE OWED MONEY
TO WERE THE AWAKUSU.
SO THEY SENT HIM TO ME SO I
COULD DIG UP A LITTLE DIRT ON
THE GIRL’S FAMILY.
OH! HI, THERE.
HE TOOK THE BAIT, HOOK, LINE,
AND SINKER.
I KNEW HARUNA WAS SAIKA, OR AT
LEAST A VARIATION.
I HAD PLANNED TO CORNER HIM AND
SAY SOMETHING LIKE, "HOW DARE
YOU STEAL MY MONEY?"
THEN I WAS GOING TO THREATEN HIM
AND USE HARUNA, BUT THAT’S WHEN
THE REAL SAIKA, THE ORIGINAL,
CAME ONTO THE SCENE.
SO THEN, WHAT BECAME OF
NASUJIMA?
>> STOP! GIVE ME YOUR MONEY!
>> HUH?
>> [howls]
>> MY PERSONAL PREFERENCE
WOULD’VE BEEN FOR SHIZU-CHAN TO
HAVE DIED THAT NIGHT.
BUT WHATEVER.
EVERYTHING STILL WORKED OUT THE
WAY I WANTED THEM TO.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> YOU WANNA ADD RESISTING
ARREST?
>> SO MANY COPS.
WHAT’S UP WITH ALL THAT?
>> THE MEDIA’S BLOWIN’ THIS
THING UP HUGE.
>> OH, YEAH, SOMETHING HAPPENED
IN SOUTH IKEBUKURO PARK TOO.
>> I HEARD THAT WAS JUST SOME
KIND OF TURF FIGHT.
>> OH, SO IT WASN’T THE SLASHER.
>> WHAT CAUSED ALL THAT, ANYWAY?
THAT OLD GUY SEEMED TOTALLY OUT
OF IT.
>> IT’S ODD HE COULDN’T REMEMBER
A THING.
IT’S LIKE HE’D BEEN HYPNOTIZED.
>> THE COPS STILL THINK IT WAS
JUST ANOTHER FIGHT BETWEEN THE
COLOR GANGS.
>> IT’S NOT JUST THE COPS.
[cell phone whispering]
[all phones ringing]
>> WHAT IS...
>> REALLY?
>> SO THIS GUY, HE’S LIKE, THE
LEADER OF THE DOLLARS, ISN’T HE?
>> CALM DOWN, MIKADO.
>> SO, JUST WHAT WERE YOU AFTER
ANYWAY?
>> THIS CITY HAS BEEN BROKEN
DOWN INTO THREE FACTIONS--THE
DOLLARS, THE YELLOW SCARVES, AND
THE ARMY OF THAT DEMONIC BLADE.
AND THE FIRST TWO HAVE BEEN
INFILTRATED BY SAIKA’S ARMY
BRINGING SPIES TO BOTH CAMPS.
TO BE HONEST, I’D HAVE BEEN
FINE WITH HARUNA NIEKAWA, JUST
SO LONG AS THAT ARMY OF THE
DAMNED CAME WITH HER.
BUT THAT ANRI SONOHARA IS MORE
INTERESTING.
>> SO?
>> I’M SIMPLY CREATING SPARKS
RIGHT NOW.
AND THAT’S FINE, ’CAUSE FROM
HERE THINGS WILL BEGIN TO
SMOLDER AND SMOKE ALL ON THEIR
OWN.
THE SUSPENSE IS KILLING ME!
>> YES, BUT THE YELLOW SCARVES
WERE STARTED BY A MIDDLE SCHOOL
BRAT, WEREN’T THEY?
HOW TOUGH CAN THEY REALLY BE?
>> THE FACT THAT A KID LIKE HIM
CAN PUT TOGETHER A POSSE OF
THAT SIZE AND STRENGTH MEANS
HE’S A SERIOUS THREAT.
BUT THEN AGAIN THE HEAD OF THE
YELLOW SCARVES IS SORT OF AN
ACQUAINTANCE OF MINE.
>> PLEASE, DON’T DRAG ME BACK
INTO THIS.
>> THOSE ASSHOLES ARE OUTTA
CONTROL!
COME ON, DUDE, WE CAN’T MAKE
A MOVE WITH OUT YOUR CALL.
>> YO, CALL HIM THE CHIEF.
SHOW SOME DAMN RESPECT!
>> YEAH, OKAY. I’M SORRY.
>> IT’S FINE. LET IT RIDE.
BESIDES, I’M NOT THE BOSS
ANYMORE.
I’M JUST A PLEBE NOW.
ACTUALLY, I’M JUST YOUR--
JUST YOUR AVERAGE HIGH-SCHOOLER.
YEAH, BEING A HIGH-SCHOOLER IS
ALL THAT I WANTED.
MY LIFE FINALLY HAD A LITTLE
PEACE TO IT.
THE PEOPLE I’M TIGHT WITH WERE
CLOSE TO ME, AND THINGS ONLY GOT
EDGY WHEN I WANTED THEM TO.
BUT THAT’S ALL GONE NOW.
AND THE PEOPLE WHO WENT AFTER
ANRI, THEY’RE GONNA HAVE TO
PAY.
I DON’T CARE HOW MANY SLASHERS
ARE OUT THERE, BUT WE’RE GONNA
CRUSH ’EM.
AND IF IT TURNS OUT THE DOLLARS
ARE MIXED UP IN ANY OF THIS,
THEN WE’LL CRUSH THEM TOO.
THOSE BASTARDS MANAGED TO DRAG
ME BACK.
DAMN IT.
DAMN IT!
[Butterfly by ON/OFF]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> I CAME BACK.
I REALLY DIDN’T WANT TO, BUT I
DID.
I CAME BACK FOR CLOSURE ON MY
PAST, FOR BOTH ME AND SAKI AND
THAT GUY.
NEXT TIME, OUT OF YOUR CONTROL.