[Complication
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK’D]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> HE DOES COME BY HERE
SOMETIMES, BUT THAT’S AS FAR AS
IT GOES.
>> SO, MASAOMI, IT’S BEEN A
WHILE.
>> HMM?
WHAT THE HELL’S THIS?!
>> THEN THEY GOT IN A HUGE FIGHT
WITH ANOTHER GANG AND KIND OF
FELL OFF THE MAP.
>> GUESS YOU CAN’T REALLY ASK
IZAYA ORIHARA ABOUT IT, HUH?
>> THOSE BASTARDS MANAGED TO
DRAG ME BACK.
DAMN IT.
DAMN IT!
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> SO A FRIEND OF YOURS WAS
HOSPITALIZED?
>> HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
>> I SAW YOU FROM THE WINDOW.
YOU CAME BY HERE TO VISIT EVERY
DAY.
YOUR FRIEND’S A GIRL, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, SHE’S THIS HIGH SCHOOL
CHICK I KNOW WITH GLASSES AND A
SMOKING HOT BODY.
>> DO YOU LIKE HER?
>> YEP. SO DOES MY BEST FRIEND.
WE GOT A LOVE TRIANGLE GOING ON.
>> IF YOU WERE TO INCLUDE ME,
THAT WOULD MAKE IT A SQUARE.
>> YOU AND ME ARE OVER WITH.
FINISHED. WE’RE ANCIENT HISTORY.
YOU KNOW THAT.
>> THEN WHY DID YOU COME HERE?
DO YOU WANT THINGS TO GO BACK TO
THE WAY THEY USED TO BE?
>> SORRY, I GOTTA BAIL.
>> YOU’LL BE BACK, MASAOMI.
’CAUSE THAT’S HOW IT’S SUPPOSED
TO BE.
SO GO AHEAD, FALL FOR AS MANY
GIRLS AS YOU WANT.
I HONESTLY DON’T CARE, BECAUSE I
KNOW THAT, IN THE END, THE ONLY
GIRL YOU’LL EVER TRULY LOVE
IS ME.
>> I DIDN’T HAVE TO HEAR THE
REST.
IT’S ALWAYS THE SAME THING.
SHE TELLS ME I CAN DATE ALL THE
GIRLS IN THE WORLD, BUT THAT
I’LL STILL COME BACK TO HER.
>> AND WHEN YOU COME BACK TO ME,
YOU’LL SEE THAT YOU LOVE ME ON A
MUCH DEEPER LEVEL THAN ANY GIRL
YOU’VE MET BEFORE.
>> BUT IT’S WHAT SHE SAYS NEXT
THAT I REALLY DIDN’T WANNA HEAR.
>> I KNOW IT’S TRUE, BECAUSE
IZAYA SAID SO.
>> WHEN I LOOK AT IT LIKE THIS,
I CAN’T HELP BUT FEEL THAT I’M
JUST A LITTLE BIT GOD-LIKE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT FEELS GOOD.
THREE-WAY STRUGGLES ARE FUN,
ESPECIALLY WHEN ALL THREE
LEADERS ARE SO CLOSELY
CONNECTED, AND GOD ATTACKS!
[laughs]
THE HOTTER THE HONEYMOON, THE
HIGHER THE FLAMES OF DESPAIR
ARISE WHEN IT ALL COMES CRASHING
DOWN AROUND YOU.
[laughing] LOOK, THE PAWNS BURN
LIKE GARBAGE.
ALL RIGHT THEN, LET’S SEE HOW
THE OTHER PIECES ON THE BOARD
ARE GOING TO MOVE.
THERE’S KYOHEI AND HIS GANG,
SHINRA, SIMON.
AH, YES, I GUESS SHIZUO-CHAN
WOULD BE THE KING, WOULDN’T HE?
CELTY, OF COURSE, IS QUEEN.
AND THE JOKER WOULD BE...
[sighs]
WHATEVER.
THIS IS TURNING INTO GOOD FUN.
WOULDN’T YOU AGREE?
[sirens]
[monitors beeping]
>> I HEARD SHE DIDN’T DIE.
THAT’S GOOD NEWS.
IF SHE’S ALIVE,
IT’LL ALL STILL WORK.
>> IZAYA...
>> YOU’RE A SMART GUY.
YOU KNOW FULL WELL THAT
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER
IS ENTIRELY YOUR FAULT.
AND I THINK IT’S
ADMIRABLE THAT YOU’VE BEEN ABLE
TO CONTROL YOUR EMOTIONS AND NOT
TAKE A SWING AT ME EVEN THOUGH--
>> [growls]
[grunting]
>> EXACTLY.
IT’S ONLY NATURAL FOR YOU
TO BE ANGRY AT ME.
AFTER ALL, I DID DELIBERATELY
PROVOKE YOU JUST NOW.
SO IS SHE IN A COMA?
I HOPE SHE WAKES UP.
OR MAYBE FROM YOUR POINT OF
VIEW, IT WOULD BE BETTER IF SHE
DOESN’T.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GETTING AT?
>> OH, I THINK YOU KNOW.
YOU’RE SCARED, RIGHT?
SCARED THAT, IF SHE DOES WAKE
UP, THEN SHE MIGHT BLAME YOU
FOREVER.
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND,
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN
IF SHE WERE TO DIE?
I MEAN, YOU COULD EASILY SPEND
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE FEELING
GUILTY ABOUT SOMETHING LIKE
THAT.
SO I GUESS IT DOESN’T MATTER
IF SHE LIVES OR DIES,
BECAUSE EITHER WAY, YOU’RE STILL
GONNA FEEL IT’S YOUR FAULT.
THERE’S JUST NO ESCAPING IT.
YOU CAN RUN FROM IT ALL YOU
WANT, BUT YOUR PAST WILL ALWAYS
FOLLOW YOU.
FOREVER AND EVER
AND EVER AND EVER.
DO YOU WANNA KNOW WHY THAT IS?
’CAUSE THESE ARE LONELY THINGS.
A PERSON’S PAST AND THEIR
MEMORIES CAN BE A VERY SOLITARY
BURDEN.
YOU SEE,
I PERSONALLY DON’T BELIEVE
IN GOD.
THERE’S NO REAL PROOF THAT HE
EXISTS.
EVERYONE’S FUTURE HAS
UNCERTAINTIES, BUT THE PAST,
THAT’S SOMETHING CONCRETE.
GRANTED, OUR PASTS MAY BE
COLORED BY FALLACIES
AND DELUSIONS.
BUT IF A PERSON BELIEVES IT
TO BE TRUE, THEN THE TRUTH
IS WHAT IT BECOMES.
NOW IF YOU SUCCUMB TO THIS POINT
OF VIEW AND MODEL YOUR ACTIONS
BASED ON YOUR OWN PAST,
WELL, THEN YOUR PAST ITSELF
BECOMES SORT OF GOD-LIKE,
DOESN’T IT?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU’RE
TRYING TO SAY.
>> OH, I THINK YOU DO.
YOU’LL NEVER BE ABLE TO ESCAPE
THIS GIRL.
YOUR GUILT WILL BECOME YOUR PAST
AND SHE WILL BECOME YOUR GOD.
BUT WHAT’S SO WRONG WITH THAT?
I MEAN, AFTER ALL, YOU DO LOVE
HER.
>> SEEMS YOU’VE MADE A FULL
RECOVERY, ANRI.
I’M GLAD YOU AND YOUR SEXINESS
ARE SAFE AND SOUND.
>> YOU DIDN’T NEED TO SAY
THE SEXINESS PART!
BUT HONESTLY, I’M GLAD
YOU’RE OKAY, TOO.
>> UM, THANKS, THAT’S NICE OF
YOU GUYS TO SAY.
>> HEY, YOU DON’T HAVE TO THANK
ME. JUST AS LONG AS YOU AND YOUR
SEXINESS ARE GOOD, I’M A HAPPY
MAN.
>> YEAH, I AGREE, EXCEPT FOR THE
SEXY PART.
[phone chimes]
>> WHAT’S UP?
GOTCHA, OKAY, I’LL BE RIGHT
THERE.
HANG TIGHT.
SORRY, HAVE TO SPLIT.
I GOT A FRIEND IN NEED.
>> WHAT, YOU’RE LEAVING?
>> HEY, IF YOU NEED TO BLAME
SOMEONE, BLAME MY FRIEND ALL YOU
WANT. BLAMING A PERSON IS FREE
AND IT CAUSES ME NO HARM.
IT’S JUST LIKE TWO WIVES FOR ONE
DUDE--LONG LIVE POLYGAMY!
>> POLYGA-WHAT?
>> LATES, PEEPS.
SEE YA TOMORROW!
>> [sighs]
I WONDER WHAT’S SO IMPORTANT.
>> DON’T YOU THINK MASAOMI’S
BEEN ACTING KIND OF WEIRD
LATELY?
>> HUH, REALLY?
MAYBE YOU’RE OVERTHINKING IT.
>> I NEVER ONCE MENTIONED THE
YELLOW SCARVES TO MIKADO.
MY LIFE WITH THESE GUYS AND MY
LIFE WITH MIKADO ARE BOTH VERY
REAL TO ME.
BUT IN MY MIND, IT’S LIKE
THEY’RE WORLDS APART.
WE WOULD SPEND OUR WHOLE DAY
FIGHTING.
THAT WAS THE ONLY CONNECTION WE
HAD WITH EACH OTHER.
ALL I REALLY WANTED WAS FOR
SOMEONE TO ACCEPT ME.
AND THAT’S WHEN I FIRST MET
SAKI.
>> THAT YELLOW SCARF LOOKS GOOD
ON YOU.
>> HUH?
>> YOU’RE MUCH COOLER THAN THE
RUMORS MAKE YOU OUT TO BE,
MASAOMI KIDA.
>> WELL, NOW, HOW DID YOU KNOW
WHAT MY NAME IS?
WHAT ARE YA, SOME KIND OF
CLAIRVOYANT?
IF YOU CAN REALLY READ PEOPLES’
MINDS, THEN I’M GONNA PUT YOU IN
A BAG AND TAKE YOU HOME WITH ME.
>> [giggling] OH, MY GOD, YOU’RE
SO SILLY.
SORRY, BUT IT WASN’T ME.
SOMEBODY ELSE HAS E.S.P.
>> OH, YEAH, WHO IS IT?
ONE OF YOUR FRIENDS HAVE A SIXTH
SENSE?
>> NO, BUT THIS PERSON IS JUST
AMAZING.
IT SEEMS LIKE HE KNOWS
EVERYTHING.
>> HUH?
THAT’S WHEN I FIRST MET THIS
GUY.
AND I SO WISH I HADN’T.
>> WELL, HELLO THERE, HOW DO YOU
DO?
YOUR NAME IS MASAOMI KIDA, ISN’T
IT?
>> THAT’S RIGHT. WHO ARE YOU?
>> IZAYA ORIHARA.
I’M AN INFORMATION BROKER.
I’M SORT OF LIKE THIS GIRL’S
GUARDIAN.
[laughs]
DON’T WORRY, I’M NOT HER
BOYFRIEND OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
IT’S A PLEASURE.
[indistinct chatter]
>> HEY, CHIEF.
>> I SAID DON’T CALL ME THAT.
I JUST WANT YOU TO USE MY NAME,
MASAOMI, OKAY?
>> Y-YEAH, SURE, BUT THAT SEEMS
KINDA WRONG.
WE CAN’T FIND OUT SQUAT ON THE
DOLLARS.
SOME OF OUR GUYS USED TO BE
MEMBERS, BUT EVEN THEY HAVE NO
IDEA WHO THEIR LEADER IS.
THEIR HEAD GUY DIDN’T EVEN
REVEAL HIMSELF WHEN THEY MET SIX
MONTHS AGO.
>> ARE THEY PLANNING ANYTHING?
>> WELL, THE LEADER HAS SENT OUT
A REQUEST ASKING FOR INFORMATION
ON THE SLASHER.
MAYBE THEY AREN’T BEHIND
THE SLASHER ATTACKS.
>> EVEN IF YOU’RE RIGHT,
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS DOESN’T ADD
UP.
>> YEAH.
>> ANYTHING ELSE?
>> WELL, I KNOW HORADA GOT HIS
ASS HANDED TO HIM BY THE BLACK
RIDER A WHILE BACK.
>> HMM? HORADA?
>> UH, WELL, A WHILE BACK, I WAS
BAGGING ON THIS FREAKY OLD GUY
WEARING A GAS MASK AND THE BLACK
RIDER JUST SHOWED UP.
>> THE BLACK RIDER?
>> YEAH, THERE WAS SOME KINDA
CRAZY-LOOKIN’ BLACK OOZE SEEPING
OUT OF IT.
SO, YOU KNOW...
>> I WONDER WHO THIS BLACK RIDER
PERSON REALLY IS.
>> SOME SAY IT’S PART OF THE
DOLLARS.
>> YEAH, OKAY, WHATEVER.
AND HEY, BY THE WAY, YOU GUYS
ARE OLDER THAN ME, RIGHT?
>> UH, YEAH.
>> DON’T BE BRINGING IN GUYS WHO
ARE ANY OLDER THAN YOU, THAT
CLEAR?
WE START SEEING NAMES LIKE
SO-AND-SO OF THE WHATEVER YAKUZA
AND THAT’S IT--WE’RE DONE FOR.
>> W-WELL...
>> WE’RE JUST A BUNCH OF PUNKS.
THERE MAY BE A WHOLE LOT OF US,
BUT IF WE START TANGLING WITH
THE ADULTS, THEY’LL JUST USE US
UP AND SPIT US OUT.
KIND OF LIKE...WHAT IZAYA
ORIHARA DID TO ME.
>> [grunts]
>> YO, DUDE, CHILL!
>> BACK THEN, WHENEVER I WASN’T
SURE ABOUT SOMETHING,
SAKI WOULD TELL ME TO RUN IT BY
IZAYA.
AND SO FROM TIME TO TIME, SHE’D
GET HIS INPUT ON THINGS.
>> SEE, IF YOU DO IT LIKE THIS--
>> AT FIRST, EVERYONE WAS A
LITTLE PISSED.
BUT WHEN WE FOLLOWED HIS
SUGGESTIONS, THINGS ACTUALLY
WORKED OUT OKAY.
BUT I DIDN’T TRUST HIM.
AND I NEVER GOT ANY CLOSER TO
HIM THAN I NEEDED TO BE.
>> IZAYA’S SO AMAZING.
IT’S LIKE HE KNOWS EVERYTHING.
HE’S NEVER WRONG.
>> SO IF HE TOLD YOU TO JUMP OFF
A CLIFF, WOULD YOU?
>> PROBABLY, YEAH.
>> I FELT SORRY FOR HER.
I DIDN’T KNOW WHY IZAYA HAD SUCH
A HOLD ON HER, BUT I WANTED TO
FREE HER FROM IT.
SO WHAT’S GOING ON WITH US?
ARE WE DATING?
>> YOU TELL ME. ARE WE?
>> I DON’T GET IT. WHY ARE YOU
HANGING OUT WITH A GUY LIKE ME
ANYWAY?
>> HMM...
’CAUSE I LIKE YOU.
>> DO YOU REALLY LIKE ME OR DID
IZAYA TELL YOU TO LIKE ME?
>> WELL, AT FIRST THAT WAS IT.
>> [gasps]
>> BUT HE DOESN’T MESS WITH
OTHER PEOPLES’ LOVE LIVES.
>> SO WHAT IS IT? WHY DO YOU
STILL LIKE ME?
>> ’CAUSE YOU’RE COOL.
MM, OR MAYBE IT’S ’CAUSE YOU’RE
CUTE.
AND SO WHAT ABOUT YOU?
DO YOU LIKE ME?
>> MAYBE IF YOU WEREN’T SO
FREAKISHLY DEVOTED TO IZAYA,
I MIGHT.
>> AND THAT WON’T CHANGE.
SO PERHAPS YOU CAN FIND A WAY TO
OVERLOOK THAT ONE FLAW OF MINE.
>> SO YOU DO KNOW IT’S A FLAW,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH, I DO.
BUT I’M NOT GONNA FIX IT.
>> YOU SHOULD REALLY TRY AND FIX
YOUR FAULTS.
I’LL EVEN HELP YOU.
>> [gasps]
>> AND AFTER THAT,
WE STARTED TO DATE.
NO ONE SEEMED TO HAVE AN ISSUE
WITH ME DATING SAKI.
I WAS PRETTY SERIOUS ABOUT HER.
AND THE YELLOW SCARVES WERE TOO
BUSY FIGHTING THE BLUE SQUARES
TO CARE ABOUT US.
THE BLUE SQUARES NEVER FOUGHT
FAIR.
THEY’D ONLY FIGHT GROUPS THEY
OUTNUMBERED AND THEY WOULDN’T
STRIKE UNLESS THEY KNEW THEY
COULD WIN.
OVER 100 OF MY FRIENDS WERE
ATTACKED BY THEM.
THEY WERE ALL SCARED--EVEN ME.
I WAS AFRAID I’D HAVE TO END THE
YELLOW SCARVES AND LOSE THE ONLY
PLACE I FELT I BELONGED, SO...
>> YOU SHOULD JUST ASK IZAYA
WHAT TO DO.
>> I ENDED UP RELYING ON HIM.
I WAS SCARED.
I DIDN’T KNOW WHERE ELSE TO GO.
>> WELL, HELLO THERE, COME ON
IN.
>> I TOLD MYSELF I WAS DOING
THIS FOR EVERYONE.
>> WHY DON’T WE SIT DOWN AND
HAVE A LITTLE CHAT?
>> HIS INFORMATION CHANGED THE
YELLOW SCARVES DRAMATICALLY.
HE DIDN’T JUST GIVE US TIPS ON
WHERE TO FIND THE BLUE SQUARES.
HE TOLD US EXACTLY HOW TO FIGHT
THEM.
WE STOPPED LOSING THOSE FIGHTS
AND STARTED GAINING
THE UPPER HAND.
YOUR INFORMATION IS
UN-FREAKIN’-BELIEVABLE.
AFTER A WHILE MY SUSPICIONS OF
HIM STARTED TO FADE.
I’D GOTTEN ALL CONFIDENT.
I LOVED THAT WE WERE WINNING.
BEATING THEM.
BUT...
[phone beeps]
HUH?
>> SO, THIS MASAOMI KIDA?
>> YEAH, WHO’S THIS?
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
I’M HEAD OF THE BLUE SQUARES.
IZUMII HERE.
I’VE GOT A LITTLE POP QUIZ FOR
YA!
QUESTION NUMBER ONE: WE’VE GOT A
SPECIAL GUEST HERE TODAY.
ANY IDEA WHO THAT MIGHT BE?
I’LL GIVE YA A HINT.
IT’S SOMEONE VERY, VERY
IMPORTANT TO YOU.
>> HEY!
>> TIME’S UP, YOU LOSE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR PLAYING,
AND I BET YOU’VE PROBABLY
FIGURED IT OUT BY NOW, HAVEN’T
YOU?
THAT’S RIGHT! DING DING DING.
WHAT A SMART GUY.
>> BASTARD!
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE WITH SAKI?
>> QUESTION TWO:
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOUR LITTLE
GIRLFRIEND LOOKS LIKE RIGHT
ABOUT NOW?
QUESTION THREE:
[crunching sound]
[Saki screaming and crying]
>> [gasps]
[grunts]
>> WHAT BONE DID WE JUST BREAK?
ONE MORE HINT--LET’S JUST SAY
SHE WON’T BE WALKING ANY TIME IN
THE NEAR FUTURE.
FINAL QUESTION:
IF YOU FAIL TO MEET US AT THE
PARKING GARAGE WHERE YOU LAST
TRAPPED US IN 20 MINUTES,
GUESS WHAT’LL HAPPEN TO THIS
PRETTY LITTLE GIRLFRIEND OF
YOURS.
[dial tone]
>> [growls]
I HAD SCREWED UP.
AND IN A MAJOR WAY.
ALL ALONG I THOUGHT THIS WAS
NOTHING MORE THAN A BUNCH OF
JUNIOR HIGH KIDS GOING AT EACH
OTHER.
BUT IT WASN’T.
IT WAS WAR.
AND THE PERSON WHO’D STARTED THE
WHOLE THING WAS ME.
PICK UP!
PICK UP, DAMN IT.
>> THE PERSON YOU ARE TRYING
TO REACH--
>> COME ON!
>> HEY, IZUMII, IT LOOKS LIKE
THE CHICK FAINTED.
>> AW, WHAT’S THE FUN IN THAT?
WE ONLY BROKE HER LEG IN A FEW
PLACES.
>> I RAN TO HER AS FAST AS I
COULD.
MY PLAN WAS TO GO THERE AND KILL
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM WHO
MADE HER SCREAM LIKE THAT.
[dial tone]
>> THE PERSON YOU--
>> THAT’S RIGHT, THE YELLOW
SCARVES.
ALL OF US ARE GETTING TOGETHER
TO PUT A BEAT DOWN ON THEIR
LEADER.
>> I SAID I WANT NO PART OF
THIS.
>> DUDE, LISTEN.
WE’VE, LIKE, GOT HIS GIRLFRIEND
KIDNAPPED RIGHT NOW.
SHE’S JUST A KID, BUT SHE’S
TOTALLY HOT.
I’M TELLING YOU, MAN, IT’LL BE
SWEET!
>> KIDNAPPED? I SEE.
WELL, IF THAT’S THE CASE,
I’M IN.
>> TOLD YA! THIS SHIT IS JUST
TOO GOOD TO PASS UP.
>> AND WHEN YOU WAKE UP, TELL
THAT BASTARD IZUMII THAT I’M
DONE WITH HIM.
>> [groans]
[tires squealing]
>> I FROZE.
EVERYTHING I’D FELT ON THE WAY
THERE WAS GONE.
WHY?
SAKI WAS IN DANGER, AND I
COULDN’T MOVE.
WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT AM I SO SCARED OF?
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THAT I COULD DO
ANYTHING FOR SAKI!
I WAS POWERLESS.
JUST ANOTHER JUNIOR HIGH KID.
>> YOU KNOW, I DON’T REALLY
CARE, BUT DO YOU THINK SHE’S
GONNA DIE?
>> NAH, SHE’S NOT BLEEDING, SHE
AIN’T GONNA DIE.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> all: HUH?
>> WELL, WELL, WELL--
WHOA, YOU GUYS REALLY DID KIDNAP
THE GIRL.
>> WELL, IT’S JUST YOU, WALKER.
WHERE THE HELL’S KADOTA AT?
>> UNLIKE IN THE MOVIES AND
MANGA, NO HELP CAME FOR THE POOR
GIRL AND ONLY A TERRIBLE DARK
FATE LAY BEFORE HER.
AND SO THIS GOT ME TO THINKING.
>> EH?
>> IF A HERO WERE TO SUDDENLY
COME OUT OF NOWHERE AND SAVE
THIS POOR DAMSEL IN DISTRESS,
THEN MAYBE THE REAL WORLD WOULD
GO ALL 2D AND TURN INTO AN ANIME
WHERE I WOULD THEN BECOME THE
TOTAL SUPERHERO SAVIOR-TYPE WITH
SPECIAL POWERS THAT LETS ME GET
ALL THE HOT CHICKS AND BUILD THE
MASSIVE HAREM I’VE ALWAYS
DREAMED OF!
>> THAT DUDE’S JUST AS FREAKY AS
EVER.
>> [vocalizing triumphantly]
WE’RE ABOUT TO EMBARK ON
"OPERATION LET’S TURN REALITY
INTO A BITCHIN’ ANIME STORY BY
WAY OF A HAPPY ENDING."
BANZAI!
[shouting]
>> GET IT OFF, GET IT OFF!
>> HUH?
[tires squeal]
>> COME ON, GET IN.
>> [yells]
DAMN IT, KADOTA!
>> WE PROBABLY SHOULDN’T TRY
TO MOVE HER TOO MUCH.
SHE NEEDS TO GO TO A HOSPITAL
IMMEDIATELY.
>> SO ARE YOU GUYS SURE THAT
YOU’RE COOL WITH THIS?
>> OUR LOYALTY LIES WITH YOU,
NOT THOSE GUYS.
WE COULD CARE LESS ABOUT THE
BLUE SQUARES.
>> PERSONALLY I’VE ALWAYS FELT
IZUMII AND HORADA WERE A BUNCH
OF ASSHOLES.
>> YEP, EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID.
>> IT’D BE WAY COOLER IF YA
THREW IT OUT THE WINDOW.
>> SIT BACK DOWN. THE ONLY
PEOPLE WHO LITTER ARE LOSERS.
HM?
>> SAKI EVENTUALLY CAME TO.
AND THANKS TO HER TESTIMONY, THE
HEAD OF THE BLUE SQUARES,
IZUMII, WAS ARRESTED.
THE BLUE SQUARES GOT WEAKER AND
FELL APART.
>> HEY.
YOU’RE KIDA--WITH THE YELLOW
SCARVES, RIGHT?
>> YEAH. WHO ARE YOU GUYS?
>> WELL...I’M NOT SURE HOW TO
EXPLAIN IT.
YOU SEE, MY NAME IS KADOTA.
>> OH, RIGHT, I HEARD ABOUT YOU.
YOU GUYS DECIDED TO GO AGAINST
YOUR GANG AND STEPPED UP TO
SAVE SAKI.
SO, UH...I OWE YOU A BIG THANKS.
>> NO WORRIES.
ACTUALLY WE WERE UP THERE JUST
NOW, TALKING TO HER.
SHE SAID THAT YOU HADN’T BEEN
BY YET.
>> YEAH, WELL, THAT’S MY
BUSINESS, NOT YOURS.
>> I HAVE A MESSAGE TO GIVE YOU.
SHE CAN SEE YOU PRETTY WELL FROM
THE WINDOW IN HER ROOM.
SHE SAID TO TELL YOU THANKS FOR
COMING THIS FAR.
I TOLD HER THAT YOU DID YOUR
BEST TO SAVE HER, BUT THE BLUE
SQUARES AMBUSHED YOU AND YOU
WEREN’T ABLE TO GET TO HER IN
TIME.
LOOK, IT DOESN’T SEEM LIKE SHE’S
MAD AT YOU, OKAY?
SEE YA AROUND.
>> WHY?
WHAT DID YOU TELL HER THAT FOR?
I DIDN’T ASK YOU TO DO THAT!
>> AND IF YOU HAD TOLD ME NOT
TO, I WOULD’VE STILL TOLD HER
ALL THAT ANYWAY.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT REALLY
HAPPENED, RIGHT?
I-I RAN AWAY.
WHEN I GOT CLOSE TO HER, I JUST
FROZE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
AND IT SEEMS TO ME LIKE YOU’RE
STILL RUNNING FROM HER NOW,
AREN’T YA?
>> SO WHAT?
WHAT ELSE AM I SUPPOSED TO DO,
LIE TO HER?
I RAN AWAY.
I JUST LEFT HER THERE!
>> YO, KEEP IT TOGETHER, KID.
IF YOU FEEL GUILTY ABOUT RUNNING
AWAY, THEN LYING TO HER IS THE
PAIN YOU’LL JUST HAVE TO
LEARN TO LIVE WITH, GOT IT?
THAT’S THE LEAST YOU CAN DO TO
MAKE IT UP TO THIS GIRL.
AND IF YOU DON’T WANNA LIE TO
HER, THEN STOP RUNNING.
IT’S TIME YOU FACE WHAT YOU’RE
AFRAID OF AND TELL HER THE
TRUTH.
IF YOU WANNA RUN FROM YOUR PAST,
FINE.
BUT WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON’T RUN FROM THE PRESENT OR,
WORSE, YOUR FUTURE.
>> CHECK IT OUT, KYOHEI JUST
SAID SOMETHING REALLY COOL!
>> TOTALLY!
I THINK WE SHOULD START CALLING
HIM POET POE-TAN NOW!
>> I NEVER DID FACE HER.
I TRIED.
I WENT THERE MANY TIMES.
I WAS JUST GONNA TELL HER THAT
WE SHOULD BREAK UP.
BUT I COULDN’T DO IT.
THEN I LEFT THE YELLOW SCARVES.
>> YOU DECIDE WHICH HIGH SCHOOL
YOU’RE GONNA GO TO YET?
>> YEAH, RAIRA ACADEMY.
IT’S CLOSE.
I KEPT SAYING HOW GREAT RAIRA
WAS.
I WAS LONELY.
AND WHEN I WAS TALKING WITH
MIKADO, I FELT BETTER.
YOU SHOULD COME, TOO.
AND THEN THE TWO OF US BECAME
TIGHT AGAIN.
I ALSO MET ANRI.
I DIDN’T THINK ANYTHING WOULD
CHANGE THIS QUIET LITTLE HIGH
SCHOOL LIFE I HAD.
BUT...
DAMN THEM. DAMN ALL THOSE
BASTARDS FOR MAKING ME COME BACK
TO THIS PLACE!
I NEVER WANTED TO COME BACK.
>> YOU’LL NEVER BE ABLE TO
ESCAPE THIS GIRL.
YOUR GUILT WILL BECOME YOUR PAST
AND SHE WILL BECOME YOUR GOD.
>> HE WAS RIGHT.
THAT IS WHY I’M HERE.
THE SLASHER HURT ANRI AND MY
FRIENDS SO I WILL DESTROY IT.
IF THE SLASHER IS WITH THE
DOLLARS, THEN I’LL TAKE THEM
DOWN, TOO.
THIS TIME, NOTHING WILL STOP ME.
THIS TIME, I WILL--
[running footsteps]
>> WHO’S THERE?
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> SOME GIRL OUT THERE WAS
SPYIN’ ON US.
THEY’RE AFTER HER NOW.
>> A GIRL?
>> YOU THINK IT’S THE DOLLARS?
>> CATCH HER, BUT DON’T HURT
HER. I WANNA TALK TO HER.
>> GOT IT.
>> I’LL GO AROUND THE BACK.
I SHOULDN’T HAVE ANY DOUBTS
ABOUT THIS.
IT’S WHY I CAME BACK.
SO THEN...
I DON’T GET IT.
WHAT’S EATING AT ME?
WHY AM I SO UNEASY?
>> [panting]
[crying out]
WHY? WHY?
WHY IS MASAOMI--
[rain falling]
[Butterfly by ON/OFF]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> THE GIRL RUNS.
SHE RUNS ON AND ON, TRYING TO
ESCAPE THE SHADOWS THAT FOLLOW
HER, TRYING TO ESCAPE THE CRUEL
TRUTH SHE JUST LEARNED.
NEXT TIME, ANARCHY.