[Complication
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK’D]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> I SEE A LOT MORE PEOPLE
AROUND THE CITY ARE WEARING
YELLOW NOW.
>> THE YELLOW SCARVES, RIGHT?
>> HEY, DID YOU GUYS HEAR?
EVERYBODY’S SAYING THAT THE
DOLLARS ARE ACTUALLY THE
SLASHER.
>> C’MON, MAN, WE CAN’T DO
ANYTHING WITHOUT YOU.
>> SO HOW IS HE?
>> HE DOES COME BY HERE
SOMETIMES, BUT THAT’S AS FAR AS
IT GOES.
>> WOULDN’T YOU AGREE THAT THE
AIR IN TOKYO IS FILTHY?
>> all: PARASITE.
PARASITE.
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
♪ ♪
>> DID YOU HEAR?
RUMOR IS SOME STUDENTS FROM
RAIRA ACADEMY WERE ATTACKED BY
THE SLASHER.
>> HUH, REALLY?
>> THAT’S SCARY.
>> THIS STUFF IS WAY SERIOUS,
GUYS.
THEY SAY IT WAS SOME FRESHMAN
GIRL.
>> SORRY, GOTTA MAKE A CALL AWAY
FROM KEYBOARD.
>> DON’T WORRY.
IT DOESN’T SOUND LIKE IT’S
YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
>> THANKS BUT I’M STILL KINDA
WORRIED.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHERE THE ATTACK
HAPPENED?
>> TOTALLY, IT WAS NEAR THE EAST
IKEBUKURO SUBWAY STATION,
RIGHT NEXT TO THE FREEWAY.
WITH ALL THE COP CARS THAT ARE
THERE RIGHT NOW, FINDING IT
SHOULD BE NO BIG DEAL.
>> REALLY?
HEY, SORRY, I HAVE TO GO.
>> SETTON, ARE YOU
RUBBERNECKING?
AH, COME ON!
SORRY, GUYS, I GOTTA GO.
>> WHAT?
YOU GET A HOLD OF YOUR
GIRLFRIEND?
>> SHE’S AT THE POLICE STATION
RIGHT NOW.
SOUNDS LIKE SHE MIGHT HAVE EVEN
SEEN PART OF IT.
I SHOULD GO SEE HER.
>> OH, GUESS I’LL GO TOO.
[computer beeping]
>> THE SLASHER.
THE PERPETRATOR OF THIS
BLOODTHIRSTY CRIME HAD A CLOSE
CONNECTION WITH ONE GIRL’S FATE.
MY OWN PAST WAS TIED TO ALL
THIS AS WELL.
BUT I HAD ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA AT
THE TIME.
[computer beeping]
[door opens]
>> I’M BACK!
HUH?
[shower hissing]
[laughs]
IT’S TIME FOR YOU TO WELCOME ME
BACK...
GET READY...
CELTY, I’M HOME NOW.
HUH?
OOH!
HI, HONEY.
[horrified scream]
[sighs]
>> WHAT’S WRONG?
>> I HAVE SEEN THE FACE OF HELL.
>> HUH?
THE FACE OF WHAT?
>> DON’T MAKE ME TALK ABOUT IT.
I JUST WANT TO FORGET.
>> OH, I’M A NEW MAN.
>> WILL YOU TAKE THAT DAMN
MASK OFF, AT LEAST WHEN YOU’RE
TAKING A SHOWER?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
TOKYO’S AIR IS SO FILTHY I CAN
NEVER TAKE THIS OFF.
BY THE WAY, CELTY, NICE WORK
YESTERDAY.
BUT TELL ME, JUST WHO WERE THOSE
YELLOW-KERCHIEFED HOOLIGANS
SWEARING AT ME LAST NIGHT?
>> THEY WOULD BE THE YELLOW
SCARVES.
THEY STARTED SHOWING UP RIGHT
AFTER YOU LEFT FOR THE STATES.
HOWEVER, I THOUGHT THEY WERE
TRYING TO LAY LOW AFTER THAT
FIGHT THEY HAD WITH THE BLUE
SQUARES.
>> WELL, I HOPE ALL THOSE GANGS
DESTROY EACH OTHER AND THEN DIE
IN THE SEWERS.
>> DON’T BE ABSURD.
>> LISTEN, YOU REALLY OUGHT TO
PAY CELTY FOR GETTING YOU BACK
HERE SAFE AND SOUND.
SHE DIDN’T HAVE TO DO THAT, YOU
KNOW.
>> HMMM.
PUT IT ON MY TAB.
>> YOUR CREDIT IS NO GOOD HERE.
>> GUESS I’LL JUST HAVE TO SKIP
OUT ON MY BILL THEN.
WHOOPS!
I WAS JUST TESTING YOU, CELTY.
THAT’S ALL.
IF YOU RELEASE ME, THEN I CAN--
[painful scream]
HEY, THEY’RE POKING ME!
THEY’RE POKING ME!
THOSE SHADOWY THINGS ARE POKING
ME!
SHINRA, CAN’T YOU SEE I’M IN
GRAVE DANGER HERE?
[groans]
IF YOU WERE TRULY MY SON, YOU
WOULD KNOW THE ANTIDOTE FOR THIS
SITUATION.
>> OF COURSE I DO.
>> [groans]
>> PLEASURE DOING BUSINESS.
>> YOU’RE NOT GETTING AN
INHERITANCE.
REMEMBER THAT.
>> FINE, I DON’T NEED IT.
>> [sighs]
I SEE THIS MONSTER HAS MADE YOU
INTO HER SLAVE.
>> IF THAT’S WHAT CELTY WANTS, I
HAVE NO PROBLEM AT ALL BEING HER
SLAVE.
>> WHAT?
OH, GOODNESS GRACIOUS, DON’T
TELL ME THIS IS TRUE.
ARE YOU ACTUALLY IN LOVE WITH MY
SON, CELTY?
I ALWAYS KNEW MY BOY WAS WEIRD
ENOUGH TO BE ATTRACTED TO YOU,
BUT ARE YOU REALLY IN LOVE WITH
HIM TOO?
>> I AM.
>> CELTY!
I’M SO HAPPY THAT YOU’RE BEING
HONEST ABOUT OUR RELATIONSHIP.
I’M ECSTATIC.
[moans]
I NEVER THOUGHT THIS DAY WOULD
EVER COME TO FRUITION.
IT’S FANTASTIC!
A SITUATION THAT STARTED OUT SO
LONG AGO AS UNREQUITED LOVE HAS
BLOSSOMED INTO A HEALTHY
RELATIONSHIP WE CAN NOW SHARE
WITH OTHERS.
MY HEART IS BURSTING WITH JOY
RIGHT NOW!
>> SHUT UP!
YOU’RE EMBARRASSING ME.
>> [muffled] YOUR AFFIRMATION OF
LOVE HAS MADE ME THE HAPPIEST
MAN ON THE PLANET.
>> [coughs]
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK I WILL
ALLOW THIS RELATIONSHIP?
>> WHAT’D YOU SAY?
>> YOU’RE AN UNINVITED GUEST
TRYING TO BLEND IN WITH HUMAN
SOCIETY.
ARE YOU AWARE OF THE FACT THAT
YOU ARE COMMONLY REFERRED TO AS
A MONSTER?
>> OF COURSE.
>> "OF COURSE," SHE SAYS.
>> SO WHAT?
I FAIL TO SEE THE PROBLEM.
>> [sighs]
IT SEEMS MY PLAN TO POINT OUT
THAT SHE’S A SOCIAL MISFIT HAS
FAILED MISERABLY.
>> SAYS THE MAN WHO WEARS A
GASMASK EVERYWHERE.
MORE IMPORTANTLY...
SHINRA SAYS HE LIKES ME EXACTLY
AS I AM.
>> HUMPH!
FINE!
I’LL ALLOW IT.
HOWEVER, IT IS ONLY ON ONE
CONDITION.
YOU HAVE TO CALL ME FATHER!
>> SHUT UP!
>> REGARDLESS, CELTY.
YOU REALIZE WITHOUT YOUR HEAD,
YOUR MEMORIES WILL NEVER RETURN.
YOUR REMEMBRANCE OF YOUR LIFE
AS A DULLAHAN IN YOUR NATIVE
IRELAND WILL BE GONE FOREVER.
>> WELL, THERE’S NOTHING I CAN
DO ABOUT THAT.
>> WE’RE GOING TO MAKE NEW
MEMORIES.
A WHOLE LOT OF THEM TO REPLACE
THE ONES YOU’VE LOST.
>> SHINRA...
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY WE START
PLANNING THE WEDDING?
I’M GOING TO NEED YOUR
MEASUREMENTS FOR THE WEDDING
DRESS.
BUT FIRST YOU’RE GOING TO NEED
TO REMOVE THOSE SHADOWY CLOTHES.
[groans]
>> THAT BOY’S ALWAYS BEEN A
SICKO.
HE ENJOYED THOSE DISSECTIONS A
TAD TOO MUCH.
>> HERE CLEARLY GETS THAT FROM
YOU.
>> I TOLD YOU TO CALL ME FATHER.
[sighs]
UNBELIEVABLE...
I JUST MADE THIS RULE AND YOU
HAVE ALREADY FORGOTTEN IT.
IT WAS THAT KIND OF NEGLIGENT
BEHAVIOR, CELTY, THAT ALLOWED ME
TO STEAL YOUR HEAD--
>> HUH?
>> UH...
OH, DANG IT, DANG IT, DANG IT,
DANG IT!
>> WAIT A SECOND.
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
>> WHAT SHOULD I DO?
I JUST SPILLED THE BEANS ON THE
BIGGEST SECRET OF ALL.
IT’S OKAY.
CELTY’S A DINGBAT.
SHE’LL PROBABLY FORGET IT IN A
SECOND.
>> WHAT?
>> RINGY, DINGY CELTY.
SILLY, DINGY CELTY.
>> THAT’S ENOUGH!
SHUT IT ALREADY!
>> IT’S QUITE EASY TO AVOID THE
ATTACKS OF A DINGY, CLUMSY GIRL.
>> I WILL NOT LET YOU TAUNT
CELTY EVEN IF YOU ARE MY FATHER.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT!
I’LL TELL YOU EVERYTHING.
I SUPPOSE THERE’S NO POINT IN
HIDING IT NOW.
YES, THE CULPRIT WHO STOLE YOUR
HEAD AND GAVE IT TO THE
PHARMACEUTICAL GIANT IS NONE
OTHER THAN YOURS TRULY.
>> WELL DON’T BRAG ABOUT IT.
>> WHATEVER.
NOW COME WITH ME.
I HAVE SOMETHING I WANT TO SHOW
YOU.
HA!
>> both: HUH?
>> DID HE JUST LEAVE?
>> AH!
OH, YOU’RE NOT GETTING AWAY YOU
CREEPY OLD LECH!
[motorcycle roars]
>> SHE GONE?
[laughs]
MY PLAN TO JUST PUSH THE
ELEVATOR BUTTON WORKED LIKE A
CHARM.
I’LL RETRIEVE MY LUGGAGE LATER.
FAREWELL!
>> DAMN IT.
WHERE’D HE GO?
HUH?
>> OH, HEY THERE, CELTY.
>> EVERYTHING OKAY?
YOU SEEM A BIT OUT OF IT.
>> WELL, I WAS JUST SORT OF LOST
IN THOUGHT.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
YOU LOOK KINDA DOWN.
WHAT IS IT?
>> [laughs]
IT’S ABOUT THE SLASHER.
PEOPLE ARE SPREADING THIS
STRANGE RUMOR ALL OVER THE
INTERNET RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT STRANGE RUMOR?
>> WELL, THEY’RE SAYING THAT THE
DOLLARS ARE BEHIND THE SLASHER
ATTACKS.
>> THEY CAN’T BE.
YOU DON’T BELIEVE THAT, DO YOU?
>> NO, OF COURSE I DON’T.
BUT IF THIS RUMOR SPREADS, I GOT
THIS SINKING FEELING THAT
SOMETHING BAD IS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
ESPECIALLY NOW WHEN THINGS ARE
STARTING TO GET TENSE BETWEEN
THE DOLLARS AND THE YELLOW
SCARVES.
>> HE’S RIGHT.
THE BALANCE IN THIS CITY IS AT A
TIPPING POINT RIGHT NOW.
MIKADO, I’LL LOOK INTO THE
SLASHER INCIDENTS MYSELF, OKAY?
>> REALLY, CELTY?
>> NOW YOU SHOULD GET GOING.
YOU ZONE OUT TOO LONG AROUND
THIS PLACE, SOMEONE’S ONLY GONNA
TO END UP MUGGING YOU.
>> YEAH...
GOOD POINT.
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
>> THE SLASHER?
SORRY, NO CLUE.
>> I SEE.
>> LISTEN...
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
YOU SHOULDN’T BE BUSTIN’ YOUR
ASS SO HARD FOR THE DOLLARS.
>> WELL, I’M NOT DOING THIS JUST
FOR THE DOLLARS.
>> I’VE GOT A SCORE TO SETTLE
WITH WHOEVER’S BEHIND ALL THIS.
[metallic whoosh]
>> HM.
IF I ACTUALLY HAD A HEAD, I’D BE
DEAD NOW.
>> DUMBASS...
>> HUH?
>> ANYONE WHO CALLS YOU A
DUMBASS IS A BIGGER DUMBASS,
AND SINCE I KNOW I’M A DUMBASS,
I’LL SAY IT!
DUMBASS!
>> WHY DIDN’T YOU TELL ME THIS?
I’LL KILL ’EM.
WHOEVER IT IS, I’LL KILL ’EM
DEAD!
I’LL KILL ’EM DEADER THAN DEAD!
>> WAIT, CALM DOWN.
I’M THE HEADLESS RIDER.
NOTHING HAPPENED TO ME.
>> NO, NO, NO!
THAT’S NOT THE POINT.
IF SOMEONE PULLS A KNIFE ON YOU,
THEN YOU HAVE TO KILL THE
BASTARD!
KILL, KILL, KILL, KILL...
>> WHAT ABOUT YOUR JOB?
YOU’RE JUST ON A BREAK RIGHT
NOW.
>> WHO THE HELL CARES?
>> LISTEN, IT’S ALL RIGHT.
I’M NOT GONNA LET YOU GET FIRED
BECAUSE OF ME.
BESIDES IF I’M GOING TO GO AFTER
THE SLASHER, I NEED TO GET SOME
INFORMATION FIRST.
SO BEFORE YOU DO ANYTHING RASH,
LET ME GET ALL THAT IN ORDER.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN.
FINE, BUT DO IT QUICK, OKAY?
KILL, KILL, KILL, KILL, KILL...
>> THERE WAS A REASON I LEFT
SHIZUO ALONE FOR A WHILE.
>> WELL, NOW...
I’M GLAD THAT YOU DECIDED TO
COME AND SEE ME.
SO TELL ME, DID YOU EVER FIND
YOUR HEAD?
>> THAT’S NOT WHY I’M HERE.
I’LL MAKE THIS QUICK.
I WANT TO KNOW ABOUT THE
SLASHER.
>> I’LL ONLY CHARGE YOU THREE
BILLS FOR THAT.
I’M GUESSIN’ YOUR CLOTHES AND
WALLET ARE MADE OF THAT SHADOWY
STUFF TOO.
SO IF THAT’S THE CASE, IF I WERE
TO SHINE A REALLY BRIGHT
SPOTLIGHT ON YOU, WOULD I BE
ABLE TO SEE YOU NAKED?
>> WANNA TRY IT?
>> NO, NOT REALLY.
SEE, UNLIKE A CERTAIN
UNDERGROUND DOCTOR WE BOTH KNOW,
I’M NO PERVERT.
I CAN’T GET IT UP FOR A CHICK
WITHOUT A HEAD OR EVEN A CHICK
WITHOUT A BODY.
>> SAY WHAT YOU WANT ABOUT ME.
BUT INSULT SHINRA AGAIN AND IT
WON’T GO WELL.
>> [laughs]
SO YOU TWO ARE IN LOVE.
YOU KNOW I WONDER...
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF ANOTHER
DULLAHAN WERE TO COME ALONG?
SHINRA MIGHT FALL FOR HER IN A
SECOND.
>> I’D LIKE TO THINK THAT’S NOT
POSSIBLE.
HOWEVER, IF IT DID HAPPEN...
>> YOU’D KILL SHINRA AND THEN
YOURSELF?
>> NO, I JUST WOULDN’T LET
ANOTHER HEADLESS WOMAN GET CLOSE
TO HIM.
I MEAN, I REALLY DO LOVE HIM.
>> [laughs]
SURE DIDN’T SEE THAT COMING.
YOU’RE BECOMING MORE AND
MORE HUMAN EVERY DAY.
JUST BE CAREFUL, THOUGH.
I’D HATE FOR YOU TO REALIZE ALL
THIS ATTENTION YOU’VE PUT TOWARD
BECOMING MORE HUMAN HAS CREATED
A MUCH BIGGER GAP BETWEEN YOUR
HEAD AND YOUR NECK.
>> I’LL WORRY ABOUT THAT ONCE I
GET MY HEAD BACK.
TO BE HONEST, I’VE BEEN THINKING
I DON’T REALLY NEED IT ANYMORE.
ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH ABOUT THIS.
TELL ME WHAT YOU KNOW ABOUT THE
SLASHER.
DON’T TAKE MY MONEY AND THEN
TELL ME YOU DON’T KNOW ANYTHING.
>> DON’T WORRY, IT’S ALL GOOD.
I’VE GOT SOME INFO THAT NEITHER
THE COPS, THE MEDIA OR EVEN THE
NET KNOWS OF.
ACTUALLY, I’VE BEEN WAITING TO
SHARE IT WITH YOU.
>> WHY ME?
>> HM.
BECAUSE THERE’S A PRETERNATURAL
ELEMENT TO THE SLASHER.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF A
SWORD CALLED SAIKA?
>> SAIKA?
>> I KNOW THAT IT SOUNDS A
LITTLE ODD, BUT SAIKA IS A
DEMONIC BLADE THAT USED TO
EXIST HERE IN SHINJUKU.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN "DEMONIC
BLADE?"
LIKE THE MURAMASA?
>> YES.
IT’S A SWORD IMBUED WITH DARK
MAGIC.
>> HEY, WHAT’S GOING ON?
>> IZAYA TOLD ME ABOUT THIS
DEMONIC BLADE CALLED SAIKA.
ACCORDING TO LEGEND IT HAS A
MIND OF ITS OWN.
AND USES ITS POWER TO POSSES
HUMANS.
ONE OF THE THINGS THAT EVERY
VICTIM HAS MADE MENTION OF WAS
THAT THE SLASHER’S EYES WERE
RED.
>> SO, DO YOU THINK THAT
SAIKA DID THIS?
>> YEAH.
EVERY TIME THERE’S BEEN A
SLASHER ATTACK, SOMEONE WITH THE
USER NAME SAIKA SHOWS UP ON THE
NET.
>> HUM.
>> WHAT BOTHERS ME THOUGH IS
THAT WHEN I WAS ATTACKED, I
DIDN’T SENSE IT APPROACHING AT
ALL.
IF SAIKA TRULY ISN’T HUMAN, THEN
I SHOULD HAVE FELT A PRESENCE OR
SOMETHING.
>> YES, BUT SAIKA IS JUST TAKING
OVER THEIR MINDS, THEREFORE THE
BEING THAT APPROACHED WAS MAINLY
HUMAN.
THAT WOULD EXPLAIN WHY YOU
DIDN’T SENSE A SUPERNATURAL
PRESENCE AT THE TIME.
>> SHINRA, YOU SEEM TO KNOW A
LOT ABOUT SAIKA.
>> I DO?
WELL, YOU TOLD ME TO LOOK INTO
IT, SO I DID.
ALL RIGHT, HURRY UP AND COME TO
BED.
>> I COULDN’T HELP BUT THINK
SHINRA WAS HIDING SOMETHING.
[gun cocks]
>> [gasps]
>> HELLO, WELCOME BACK.
WHEN MS. NAMNIA HERE DISAPPEARED
AFTER THE MERGER WITH NEBRACORE
I DECIDED TO DO A LITTLE
INVESTIGATING.
AND IN MY RESEARCH, I DISCOVERED
THAT SHE VISITS YOU NOW ON A
REGULAR BASIS.
SO WITH A LITTLE ENCOURAGEMENT
FROM MY TOY GUN, SHE WAS KIND
ENOUGH TO ESCORT ME IN.
>> YOUR TOY GUN?
>> OH, DID I NOT MENTION THAT?
[gunshot]
>> I WANT TO REPORT THIS BASTARD
TO THE POLICE.
>> REALLY?
WOULDN’T YOU BE THE ONES IN HOT
WATER IF THAT HAPPENS?
MY TESTIMONY MAY LEAD THE POLICE
TO SEARCH THIS ROOM, WHERE
THEY’LL FIND THE BLOODY HEAD OF
A POOR YOUNG WOMAN.
WHO KNOWS, MAYBE THAT WILL BE
EVEN BIGGER NEWS THAN THE
SLASHER CURRENTLY IS.
>> SO...
NOW I SEE WHERE SHINRA GETS HIS
LOVELY TWISTED DISPOSITION.
>> FLATTERY WILL GET YOU
NOWHERE.
TO BE HONEST, I’M IN NO RUSH TO
RECOVER THE HEAD JUST YET.
>> HUH?
>> THE EXECUTIVES AT MY COMPANY
WERE QUITE TAKEN ABACK BY
CELTY’S LITTLE TELEVISION DEBUT.
AND, NOW THEY’RE FAR MORE
INTERESTED IN STUDDING THE BODY
AT THIS POINT THAN THE HEAD.
>> WHAT?
>> SO THAT’S WHY I TOLD THE
COMPANY THAT I WOULD INVESTIGATE
THE HEAD ON MY OWN.
AFTER ALL, I THINK THE APPROACH
YOU HAVE TAKEN TO THIS UNIQUE
MATTER IS VERY INTERESTING.
IN YOUR THEORY, DULLAHANS ARE
ACTUALLY A TYPE OF VALKYRIE.
YOU’RE HOPING TO INVOLVE THE
HEAD IN SOME SORT OF STRUGGLE OR
CONFLICT...
SO YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO ROUSE IT
INTO CONSCIOUSNESS, HM?
>> WELL, I’VE TRIED MANY
APPROACHES.
BUT IF ALL ELSE FAILS I MAY HAVE
NO CHOICE BUT TO BRING THAT HEAD
INTO A WARZONE.
REGARDLESS THOUGH, I WOULD BE
HAPPY TO WORK WITH YOU ON THIS
IF THAT IS INDEED WHY YOU CAME
HERE.
>> EXCELLENT.
I’VE HAD MY EYE ON YOU FOR QUITE
SOME TIME.
NOBODY ELSE THOUGHT TO LOOK AT
THIS FROM A MYTHOLOGICAL
STANDPOINT, NOT EVEN MYSELF.
I’M VERY IMPRESSED.
>> WHY, THANK YOU.
>> BEFORE I GO, LET ME GIVE YOU
ONE PIECE OF ADVICE.
>> IF YOU DO CREATE SOME SORT OF
CONFLICT HERE IN TOKYO IN AN
EFFORT TO ROUSE CELTY’S HEAD, OR
HER SOUL, I WILL MAKE ONE
SUGGESTION.
INSTEAD OF PULLING CELTY INTO
SOMEONE ELSE’S WAR, INSTEAD
CREATE THE CONFLICT AROUND HER.
AND WHOEVER SHOWS UP FOR THE
FIGHT, THROW THEM INTO THE FIRE.
>> THAT’S MY INTENTION.
IN FACT, THINGS ARE PROGRESSING
IN THAT DIRECTION FASTER THAN I
THOUGHT.
>> ANRI...
>> I KNOW IT’S TIME FOR GYM
CLASS NOW, BUT ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I’M FINE.
>> I’VE BEEN WORRIED.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING WITH THOSE
STUDENTS WHO WERE ATTACKED THE
OTHER DAY?
DON’T TELL ME THOSE GIRLS HAVE
BEEN BULLYING YOU AGAIN.
I’M WORRIED, ANRI, REALLY
WORRIED.
WHO’S TO SAY THE SLASHER WON’T
COME AFTER YOU AGAIN?
YOU SHOULDN’T BE ALONE.
>> SEXUALLY HARASSING HER
AGAIN?
NOW THAT’S JUST PLAIN NAUGHTY,
TEACH.
>> I’M SIMPLY CONCERNED FOR
ANRI’S SAFETY, THAT’S ALL.
>> WHOA!
SO YOU GUYS ARE TIGHT!
THAT’S CRAZY DANGEROUS!
DON’T GET TOO CONCERNED FOR HER,
OR SHE JUST MIGHT TRANSFER, LIKE
MISS NIEKAWA DID.
DIDN’T THAT GIRL HAVE CLASSES
WITH YOU LAST YEAR?
HARUNA NIEKAWA?
>> [gasps]
SO THEN YOU KNOW NIEKAWA.
>> OH, JUST HER NAME.
WELL, IT’S TIME FOR US STUDENTS
TO BE HEADING HOME NOW.
>> WHO’S HARUNA NIEKAWA?
>> HEY, ANRI...
I’M BETTIN’ THAT MIKADO HASN’T
ASKED YOU OUT YET, HAS HE?
>> WHAT?
>> THOUGHT SO.
BUT YOU KNOW, HE’S CRAZY ABOUT
YOU, RIGHT?
>> I THINK MIKADO IS A NICE GUY
AND A GOOD FRIEND.
>> LOOK, MY BEST FRIEND SEEMS
GENUINELY IN LOVE WITH YOU, SO
I’M JUST GONNA BOW OUT OF THE
PICTURE FOR NOW, OKAY?
PLUS, THERE’S CHICKS ALL OVER
THE WORLD WHO DESERVE A LITTLE
TASTE OF MY LOVE, HEE-HEE.
>> MASAOMI...
ANRI...
>> WELL, SPEAK OF THE COWARD AND
THERE HE IS.
>> SORRY TO MAKE YOU GUYS WAIT.
>> WE ALMOST FOSSILIZED, YOU
TOOK SO LONG.
>> SCORE SQUARE ROOT OF THREE.
>> SQUARE ROOT OF WHAT?
YOU GOT TO BAG ON ME WITH TERMS
I KNOW LIKE MINUS 20 POINTS.
>> LATER!
>> SEE YOU GUYS TOMORROW!
>> SEE YOU TOMORROW!
>> IT’S THE BOMB, BRO.
>> JUST KEEP TELLING YOURSELF
THAT.
>> YOU FINALLY CAME.
>> CELTY?
>> HMH?
>> ABOUT SAIKA, YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT MY DAD HAD IT FOR A WHILE.
BUT HE SOLD IT TO AN ANTIQUES
DEALER A FEW YEARS AGO.
>> SHINGEN HAD IT?
WHY?
>> BECAUSE, IT SAID THAT SAIKA’S
ABLE TO CUT SOULS.
>> HUH?
>> DID HE?
>> YES.
HE’S THE ONE RESPONSIBLE.
HE USED THE SAIKA TO STEAL YOUR
HEAD.
THAT’S HOW HE CUT THE SOUL THAT
HELD YOUR HEAD AND BODY
TOGETHER.
>> [gasps]
AND YOU’VE KNOWN THIS ALL
ALONG?
>> SORT OF.
BUT ONLY FOUND OUT HE USED IT TO
TAKE YOUR HEAD WHEN I DID MY OWN
RESEARCH LATER.
I DIDN’T SAY ANYTHING AT
FIRST BECAUSE IT SEEMED LIKE YOU
WERE TRYING TO MOVE ON AND
FORGET ABOUT YOUR HEAD.
BUT...
>> LISTEN...
I NEED TO BE ALONE FOR A WHILE.
>> OF COURSE YOU DO.
>> LOVE JUST CONFUSES THINGS.
IT TURNS OUT THAT SAME NIGHT
THERE WAS A CERTAIN GIRL SAIKA
WAS LOOKING TO LOVE AS WELL.
A GIRL WHO WAS HAVING A HARD
TIME FINDING HER PLACE IN THE
WORLD.
ANRI SONOHARA.
[Butterfly by ON/OFF]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ [singing in Japanese] ♪
>> IKEBUKURO.
ALL I WAS LOOKING FOR WAS THE
SOURCE OF THIS JUNK TOWN’S
ENERGY, THE TRUTH ABOUT ITS
GREED, UNCAGED DESIRES.
NEXT TIME, DUMB LIKE A FOX.