I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
[Girl 1] Hey,
check it out!
That guy over there is,
like, unbelievably hot!
[Girl 2] Yeah! I wonder
what he's got going on?
He looks like he's on his
way to a rave or something...
You're right. He looks
like a total club kid.
Let's go talk to him!
A cool guy like that?
I'll bet we can
have some fun!
[Tohru] Winter
break is over,
and the third term has
started at school...
Wipe that smug little
smirk off your face
before I come over
there and do it for you!
Yeah, you'll be sorry
then, won't you?
And I'll make
you say it!
I'm sorry.
Shut up! You're a real
wise ass! You know that?!
At least I'm not
the noisy idiot
who's causing a scene
in front of the store...
Oh, you've done
it now, girly-boy!
We're takin'
this outside!
We're already outside,
you stupid cat.
Sorry I
took so long.
Ah... find everything
you needed?
Uh...
uh-huh...
[Tohru] It seems like Yuki
and Kyo are getting along
even worse
than usual...
It's too bad.
Especially since the wish
I made this New Year's
was that the two of them would
start getting along better...
But I guess...
I guess it didn't really have
much of an effect, did it...
You know, you are starting
to get on my nerves.
Oh yeah? So why don't
you try to do something
about it,
girly boy--
Leeks...
Kyo!
There. That should keep him
quiet for a little while.
Hey! I'm out of the tub...
Who's in next? Yuki?
I think I'll
skip it today.
Eww... How can you
stand to be so dirty?
Just once, I'd like to
knock him through the roof...
What's wrong? Are
you feeling okay?
Well... No... I think I'm
coming down with a cold.
A cold?!
You do have a
bit of a fever.
[Shigure] Well, it's best
to treat these things early.
Take some medicine, get
some rest, all that...
I think I have just
the thing here...
Maybe you should stay
home from school tomorrow...
No, I'm all right... It
won't have to come to that.
Are you sure? We are supposed
to do our endurance run...
Oh, so they
still have those?
It almost
seems cruel,
making you kids run
around in the cold...
An endurance
run, huh?!
[Tohru] Yes... You
mean you didn't know?
The endurance run...
a set distance...
a certain time
to beat...
In other words...
It's a race!
All right,
rat boy!
Tomorrow we're going to
find out who's the fastest!
Um, Kyo. Yuki's starting
to come down with a cold...
So you better give
him something to eat
and put
him to bed!
He's not gettin'
out of this one!
Here take one of these... And
all joking aside, remember,
if you strain your body
too much, you'll transform.
Don't
overdo it.
I know...
I'm not so sure
this is a good idea.
I'd feel
much better
if he stayed home tomorrow
and got some rest...
Hey
Yuki...
...how are you
feeling today?
Don't worry... I think I'll
be able to manage... Besides...
If I don't
do this,
that stupid cat will never
let me hear the end of it...
You know, I don't believe I've
seen Miss Uotani here today...
Right. She thought this
might be a good day to skip.
Hana's here,
though!
[Coach] All right,
girls! You're up first!
Everybody make your way to
the starting line at the gate.
Well,
gotta run!
Good luck.
Hey Hana, let's do
our best today for Uo
since she's
not here...
All right... I've never
been very good at running,
but since
you asked,
I will try
my hardest.
Okay, on your
marks... Get set!
Oh! Hana, what's the
matter? Are you okay?
Tohru, I'm sorry. I
can't run any further...
I've done
my best,
but now I've reached
the edge of my limits...
And don't worry, I'll
be right behind you
the whole time...
only walking.
Hana...
Walk, crawl, I don't care.
Just start, Miss Hanajima!
I wonder if Hana's doing
all right back there...
I guess it's about time the
boys were starting, too...
I hope Yuki really is
okay, like he says...
Huh? What's that?
That white hair!
An old man?!
Sir!
What's wrong?
Wait... he looks
like he's my age!
I'm sorry! I just thought,
well, your hair is so white,
I thought you
were an old man
that had fallen
down or something!
I mean, not that you
look like an old man--
Have you ever heard of a
place called Sohma House?
Oh yeah! Eat my
dust, rat boy!
Shut up.
What do they think this
is, the 100-meter dash?
That's just
stupid...
Eh, Sohma House?
So then...
...by any chance, are
you a Sohma? Maybe?
That's right. So
you know it, then?
Oh, y- yes! I'm, um, I'm
pleased to meet you!
I'm Tohru--
uh?
What
is it?
He's
coming.
Wow, so if he's part
of the Sohma family,
then maybe he's part
of the zodiac, too!
Um... What
are you doing?
Got him.
Kyo! Are
you hurt?!
Kyo!
Miss Honda?
What the hell are you
doing?! Dammit!
I was winning
and everything!
If I hadn't
tripped you,
you wouldn't have
stopped, now would you.
Haru?
By the way, what I just
did was very dangerous...
And if that had been
anyone other than Kyo,
they'd probably had
been hurt pretty badly.
So, don't try
this at home.
Don't try it here! Who
are you even talking to?!
So, now
it's Haru...
They just keep showing
up, don't they.
Shouldn't you
be at school?
Yeah... well, I
actually left on Sunday
with the intention
of coming here,
but I was swept
away into the heart
of a dark,
urban wilderness.
It took me three days
to find my way out.
Why don't you just
say you got lost?
His sense of direction's
as crappy as ever...
But if you're
gonna get lost,
that's an impressive
way to do it!
Oh yeah? Well it means
he hasn't had a bath
in three
days... Gross!
Um...
Hey...
do you think we should move
somewhere off the road?
[Yuki] Mmm. That
might be wise...
Oh... this
is Hatsuharu...
He's still in his third
year of middle school,
one year
behind us.
Haru, this is
Miss Tohru Honda.
Well then, Miss Tohru Honda...
it is a pleasure to meet you.
Oh, no! The pleasure's
all mine! Really!
He's so polite.
He seems like he's a
lot more grown-up
than you'd expect from
someone in middle school...
[Kyo] So, what did you
come here for, anyway?
[Haru]
To fight.
I was planning to challenge
you at the New Year's banquet,
but you decided to skip...
So I've come to you.
Now let's
do it.
H-Hold on
a minute!
I'm right in the middle
of something here,
in case you
hadn't noticed!
I've already wasted three
days looking for you...
That's your own damn fault!
You're the one who got lost!
Um, I think this
conversation
just took a turn
for the worse...
This could
get ugly.
Hey, Kyo... maybe you
should just go ahead
and do what he
says before--
No! I said no,
and I mean no!
Now get outta
here! I'm busy--
You make me sick... You and
your pathetic, girly whining.
Too late.
You're not
a man.
You're a little kitty-cat,
too scared to fight!
Know what? You
can go to hell!
You little punk!!
[Kyo] What's your problem?
What did I ever do to you?!
That idiot. He just had to
go and bring out Black Haru.
B- B-
Black...?
Haru's pretty easy
to get along with,
but once he snaps,
he's uncontrollable...
That's our
nickname for him
when he's like
this: "Black Haru".
Ah... So-- what
you're saying is,
he's got the same sort
of temper as Kagura?
Not at
all...
...I'm saying he's a
thousand times worse.
Yuki. Are you comfortable?
Enjoying the show?
Hope so, 'cause I'm
coming for you next.
Oh, is
that a fact.
Get up, Kyo!
I've been up! Where
the hell were you?
I'm right here.
C'mon! Fight!
You know... this could
go on for hours.
You really don't
have to stay.
Uh...
but...
"Go away!"
"Leave me alone!"
When did you become
such a little pansy, huh?
You know, when you go Black,
you are a real bastard!
Oh yeah? Just for that,
when I'm done with you...
I'm gonna take your
little girlfriend.
What the--
You're gonna what?
Oh, you know. I'm gonna do
this, and a little of that,
and I'm definitely
gonna do that!
Huh? What is he--
This is the same
little brat
that used to get lost on
the way to the bathroom
if I didn't
take him.
And now he thinks he's some
kind of... I don't know what.
He really is a bastard
when he goes Black.
Who got him all
worked up, anyway?
Okay, I guess
that was me.
So why's he gotta
bring Tohru into this?
What's she got to
do with anything?
And what's he
talking about,
all this "I'll do this,
I'll do that" crap?
Whatever it is...
You're sick!
And if it's a fight you want,
you got it! Just bring it on!
That's more like
it, coward.
It's about time
you came around!
Miss Honda... This
really will take a while.
You should head
back if you want.
But shouldn't we... at
least try to stop them?
Hey, Saki!
Maybe you should
try runnin', huh?
No.
Come on, what's the
matter!? Hit me!
What fight are
you watching?
You haven't landed a single
punch yet! You hit me!
You got it!
Somehow, this has turned
into a fighting anime.
Um...
Excuse me...
Let's leave them
alone, Miss Honda...
It's best to let
them fight it out.
It's what they
want... Besides...
I don't know
about you,
but I'd rather not be the
one who stands between them...
It's a
little risky...
I still can't believe
this is the same Hatsuharu
I met a few
minutes ago...
He seemed like such a nice
person... and now this...
You pansy! What kind of
girly punch is that?!
I didn't even
feel it!
It almost doesn't
seem possible,
that a person can just
snap and change this much...
Then again, I'm getting the
impression that the Sohmas
have a lot of people like
this in their family...
Don't get cocky,
you brat!
Compared to Yuki,
you move like a turtle!
Heh! So what does
that make you?
You still can't beat Yuki
yourself, now can you, Loser!
And you did all that
extra training, too...
You're even worse
than a turtle!
You're a snail!
An amoeba!!
I am seriously
gonna murder you!
He's not
serious.
Oh... But...
look at him...
I've never seen Kyo
fight like this...
Yes... well... against Haru...
Kyo does seem a lot stronger...
If you ask me, they're both
a couple of fighting fools...
They've been studying martial
arts since they were...
since they
were...
Oh...
Yuki?
Yuki!
Is it an
asthma attack?
His bronchial tubes...
And you have a
fever too, don't you?
You know you're not supposed to
overdo it when you're sick...
Just lie here
for now.
Go call the main house,
and hurry! --huh?
Yuki...
This is bad... This is really
bad. He can hardly breathe.
I knew I should have tried
to make him stay home today...
You don't want the
main house, huh?
Kyo, you don't mind if we
finish our fight later...
do you?
Uh-uh...
We need to get him back
to Shigure's somehow.
Damn... I guess this means the
endurance run is over, too...
That really bites.
I was winning.
I'd say we could take a
taxi, but I don't know.
It'll be a real pain if he
transforms in the back seat.
But we have to do something!
I'll do anything!
Okay... Maybe there is
something we can do...
It's lucky for me
you're so cute...
I mean, if I'm
gonna do it,
it should be with
someone cute, right?
Hold on to the back of my
neck, so I don't change back.
It'll be easier on Yuki
if we carry him like this.
That's it...
It was a good run, but at
last it has come to an end...
You dealt me the ace.
I have a royal flush.
What,
again?!
How do you always get
all the good cards?
You guys, if you're not
going to run, go home.
So, you came all the way here
looking like that, did you?
It's not funny.
[Shigure] There. We'll let
him sleep for a while.
Looks like it was
just a mild attack.
He still has a slight fever,
but he'll be all right.
Thank
goodness!
Sorry for the scare, Tohru.
But it's really okay.
You can go back to
school now, if you want.
Oh, no-- I mean,
school is important,
but I just wouldn't
feel right going back
when I know that he's
lying here sick...
I'm sure Mom will
understand if I miss a day.
And besides-- I feel a
little bit responsible...
I should have asked
him to stay home today.
His cold might not
have gotten this bad...
I'll tell
you what.
How about I go
to the school
and pick up your
things for you.
You really don't have to
go to all that trouble...
No, no. No
trouble at all...
In the meantime, Kyo,
why don't you call Hatori?
Huh? Why do I
gotta do it?
Watch yourself, though.
Hatori's a bit
overworked these days,
so he's probably not
in the best of moods...
From what
I hear,
practically the entire family
has come down with the flu...
I'll call
him.
Where's the
phone, again?
Dammit! Put some
clothes on first!
Well, I'm off. Take good
care of Yuki while I'm gone.
Okay, and thank
you so much!
It's so nice of
him to do this.
Shigure can be so
selfless sometimes.
He's always thinking
about others...
High school girls,
high school girls!
All for me,
Mm-hm. I understand...
R-Right.
So what's Hatori
got to say?
He sounded mad at me, for
some reason... Strange, huh?
That's what happens when you
disappear for three days.
So, what now? I guess we got
that damn rat taken care of...
You ready to
finish our fight?
Nah, forget it...
You really have
gotten stronger, Kyo.
I think I need
more training.
Hold it
right there!
You think you can pick a
fight and then just walk away
whenever you feel
like it! Huh?!
Just 'cause you changed
back to "White Haru"
doesn't mean
you get--
So... you're not
"Black Haru" any more?
Uh...
no.
I'm sorry...
It's just,
you seem like a completely
different person...
How's Yuki.
He's still
sleeping.
Don't attack him while
he's passed out, Kyo.
Shut up!!
What good does it
do me if I beat him
with a cheap
trick like that?!
The day I knock that
damn rat on his tail
it's gonna be
fair and square!
Hell with it. I'm
going back to school.
Yuki and Kyo, do they still
get in fist fights every day?
No, but they
argue just about
every time they
see each other...
Huh. Well that means
they're getting along
a little better,
at least...
It wasn't
long ago,
that the idea would've
seemed pretty hopeless.
No...
Hopeless?
That's how
it seemed...
But I can tell they've
both changed since then...
There used to be so much
tension between them,
if they were in the same room
you could feel it in the air...
Things seem much
more relaxed now...
It could be because
you're here...
No, I doubt I've made that
much of a difference...
Well, I can't
prove that yet.
But I haven't been around
enough to see what's going on.
But I guess the reason
isn't really important.
I'm just glad to see
they're doing better...
Especially Yuki... He was
my first love, after all.
Nothing against Kyo. Yuki
is just very special to me...
Although, when we were
kids, I couldn't stand him.
I hated
his guts.
Oh...
Really? Why?
Because
he's the Rat.
[Haru] It's in the
old story, right?
How the Rat rode on the Cow's
back to the zodiac banquet...
I used to hate
that story
when I was a little
kid... The Cow...
...the Cow was
a stupid fool...
letting the Rat use
him like that...
That's what all the adults
used to tell me, anyway...
I know they were probably half
joking when they said it...
...still, I couldn't
help but feel
I was the one they were
laughing at, calling stupid...
And after hearing
it over and over,
I had so much anger towards
that Rat bottled up inside
I couldn't
contain it.
I started losing my temper
over the tiniest things...
I guess that's when
my "Black" personality
first began
to appear...
It got to be too much
for my parents to handle,
so they had me take
martial arts lessons,
hoping that would give
me a way to vent...
Hiya!
Your form
sucks!
It didn't really help,
like they thought it would...
I enjoyed the training
itself, but even there,
it still felt like I was
getting laughed at a lot...
And then
one day...
I happened to
bump into Yuki.
The truth is,
up until then,
I'd never even
said a word to him.
The only time we ever saw
each other was at New Year's...
But that day, seeing
him sitting there,
all of my anger began to
swell up at once. I exploded.
I hate your guts!
It's the Rat's fault
everybody
laughs at the cow!
It's the Rat's fault they call
the cow a fool, and an idiot!
It's your fault! The
dirty, mean, stinking Rat!
Well, is
it true?
About you, I mean. Is it?
Is that what you are?
Are you a fool?
No... No, I'm
not... I...
I'm not a fool...
I'm not a fool!
Mm-hmm...
I didn't
think so.
After that, I began to lose
my temper less and less.
Yuki had finally allowed
me to vent the anger
that had filled
me up for so long.
It felt as though my heart
had suddenly been set free.
I was completely surprised.
In every possible way,
Yuki was different
from the person
I'd imagined
him to be...
It's true.
Until that point,
it had never occurred
to me he could be anything
other than
the "mean rat".
And to think... If I
hadn't met him that day...
The "mean rat" is probably
all I'd see, even now.
Then I would really
would be a fool.
That's a
wonderful story.
I was surprised
today, too--
seeing Yuki next to you, with
that little smile on his face.
That was a
first for me...
He never smiled like that when
he lived at the main house...
That's why I
was thinking,
maybe it's
your influence
that's helped him
to soften up a bit...
Oh, no that can't be! I'm
sure it's something else!
I mean, I don't know
what I could have done
that would
be so great--
I'll prove
it to you.
When he
wakes up...
Uh...
Miss Honda?
Hi.
Welcome back.
That's right!
I was...
I hope I wasn't
any trouble...
No, it's
all right...
But how... how
did I get here?
Hatsuharu transformed and
carried you on his back...
Well, thank you... It
must have been a sight.
No... I didn't
mind at all.
You were asleep by
the time we got home.
And since then, I've been
telling Tohru the story
about why I
like you...
What, is that
the only thing
you could think
of to talk about?
I at least hope you didn't bore
her with too many details...
She seemed
interested...
It's okay. It was a very
nice story... 'Prince' Yuki...
Well, don't pay any
attention to Haru, he--
When he
wakes up...
Try calling him by
his nickname once...
I'll bet it
cheers him up.
There, you see... It doesn't
work at all when I say it...
[Tohru] And so, despite a
few bumps along the way,
everyone managed to
survive the endurance run...
Unfortunately, by the
end of the evening,
a few more of them had
come down with colds...
That's what happens
when you sit out
in the freezing air for
hours, playing Old Maid...
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
[Tohru] It's gonna be an
interesting Valentines day.
[Shigure]
Here! Ha'ri,
I got you some
Vaentine's chocolates!
[Kagura] A chocolate heart
stuffed full of my love,
all for you!
[Kyo] Keep it! What man
in his right mind
would eat that
girly, sugary crap!
[Tohru] I'm sorry, but, do you
really not like chocolate, Kyo?
[Kyo] Fine! I just gotta
eat it? So, I'll eat it!
[Yuki]
Idiot.