I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
[Hatori]
Since long ago,
whether by Akito or my
father before him,
I have been called upon
numerous occasions
to suppress the
memories of others.
I knew the suffering
it would cause Yuki
if I erased his young
friends' memories.
But still... I did
as was required.
[Akito] Hatori -
you're as cold as snow.
[Hatori] And so it seems...
The words Akito spoke that day-
are more true than
even he realized.
Hey! You guys,
she's gone!
I can't find
her anywhere!
If you mean Tohru, she told
us last night at dinner
that she was going over
to a friend's house
for a visit
today...
Wha...? She
did? Really?
That's what he said, or
weren't you listening.
Shut up! I mean, she hardly
ever goes out and stuff!
Well... it
goes to show
how accustomed you've gotten to
having her around the house.
Her absence
is felt...
Alas, where has our
beautiful flower now gone?
You're babbling
again.
I- it's
so big...
I guess the Sohmas really
must be a large family...
I wish I could have told
Yuki and the others
that I was
coming here,
especially after what
he said about Hatori.
And then there's
this Akito person-
to think that I might have
to meet the head of the family
all by myself...
Hi!
M-M-Momiji! I
didn't see you there!
You're right on time! You can
go ahead and let yourself in.
I hope I'm
not intruding...
Come in!
Welcome to the
House of Sohma!
Whoa...
It seems even bigger on the
inside, if that's possible...
It's like they've got
a whole town in here,
like it's its
own little world...
But it's so quiet. There's not
a single other person around.
It almost seems
like a ghost town.
And I think I'm only
making myself more nervous...
C'mon...
this way!
I'll show you the rest of
the way to Ha'ri's house.
What, you're not
scared are you?
Uh... no, of
course not...
I like Ha'ri
a lot!
I think you will too,
once you get to know him.
[Hatori] Please, relax.
Make yourself comfortable.
Oh...
okay...
So he tells me. But I
think that's going to be
a little bit easier
said than done...
A photograph?
I wonder why he
has that there?
It doesn't look like
he keeps any other
personal things in here.
And he seems
the type of person
who likes to keep a very
professional appearance...
When he said he had something
important to discuss with me,
maybe he meant that I'd
done something wrong!
I mean, if he's
concerned with appearances,
someone from a big, important
family like the Sohmas
probably doesn't want to
be associated with a girl
who used to
live in a tent...
Maybe I've offended him somehow
without even realizing it!
Tohru? You don't look like
you're feeling too good...
You want Ha'ri to look at you?
He is a doctor, you know.
No, I'm all right!
Everything's fine!
I am a
doctor, yes.
But my practice is
devoted exclusively
to the Sohma family,
and I should say,
Akito in
particular.
He suffers frequent illness
and requires much of my time...
Oh... I had
no idea...
So my time is valuable...
Right to the point, then.
Uh...
sure...
Even within the
Sohma family itself...
there are few who
know our secret
in regard to
the zodiac...
It is exceedingly rare
that a complete outsider,
such as yourself,
should come to learn of it.
Ordinarily, this would have
been corrected at once.
But thus far,
it seems Akito has made
an exception in your case.
Tell me, do you enjoy living
there, in Shigure's house?
Y- yes,
very much.
All the more reason
that you should leave.
It would be
best for you
if you had nothing further
to do with the Sohmas.
Leave Shigure's house, and
return to your own family.
That's only
reasonable, is it not?
Knowing Shigure, I doubt he
would ever say anything to you.
But there are many dark secrets
within the House of Sohma.
Life among us is
not as pleasant
as you seem
to believe...
An evil shadow looms
over this family...
That is the nature
of our curse.
Evil...?
Before you come to
regret having been involved
with the Sohmas-
leave them.
Say, Ha'ri, I want to
take Tohru outside
and show her the gardens...
That's okay, right?
C'mon, Tohru,
let's go!
Uh...
But, uh...
C'mon! It'll be fun!
I'll even show you my favorite
spot! Come on, this way!
Life among us
is not as pleasant as
you seem to believe...
An evil shadow looms
over this family...
That is the
nature of our curse.
[Momiji] It's
quiet, isn't it?
Y- yes, it is.
That's 'cause everyone's
at the main house
getting ready for New Year's.
It's a really big deal for us.
It's the one time of year
where we all get together.
So there's
a lot to do!
Know what? From that tree-lined
road outside the gate...
to the main house
over there...
everyone who lives
around here,
they're all related
to the Sohma family.
All of them?
That's incredible!
Shigure
and Yuki?
They used to live here
too, a long time ago.
The only ones who can
live inside the gates
are members of
the zodiac like me,
or people who know
about the secret.
Did you know Ha'ri can barely
see out of his left eye?
Ha'ri had a
girlfriend, once. Kana.
She worked as his
assistant for a while.
And I remember,
she was really nice.
When she found out about Ha'ri
and the zodiac y'know,
it didn't even bother her.
She just laughed about it.
They got engaged. And they
were going to get married,
but when they told Akito...
Well, he got really,
really angry and he said that
he wasn't going to allow it.
I guess his temper
got out of control,
'cause that's when he
hurt Ha'ri's eye.
[Momiji] But Ha'ri didn't
blame him, though.
And Kana- she
blamed herself.
She was convinced that
Ha'ri getting hurt like that
was all her fault. She
couldn't forgive herself.
And it gradually started
to eat her away inside.
So... Ha'ri did the
only thing he could do.
He erased
Kana's memories.
He couldn't stand to watch her
tearing herself apart over him,
so he made
her forget
that the two of them had
ever been in love...
Kana left...
Ha'ri cried...
And in spite of all that... he
still never once blamed Akito.
[Tohru]
Why?
Well... because
that's the curse.
That's why I can
understand a little bit
of what Ha'ri feels...
He doesn't want anyone else
to end up like Kana did...
He doesn't want
you to be hurt,
the same
way she was.
Huh?
Tohru?
Are you crying?
Was it me...?
Did I make you cry?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, okay?
No, that's not it...
It's just that...
I was so worried about coming
here... And the whole time...
he just wanted to help me...
he was just being kind...
But after what
he's been through,
he's the one who deserves
to be shown kindness. Not me.
I'll go get something
to warm us up, okay?
I'll be right back... You
can go inside if you want.
[Tohru] Huh?
It's snowing...
[Kana] I knew it
would snow today!
[Tohru] I'm
sorry, I...
I guess, I don't
really know anything
at all about
the Sohmas I-
[Hatori] And there's no
reason why you should.
In fact, it would be
best if you forgot
whatever it is
Momiji told you...
[Tohru]
Does that mean...
you've forgotten
about her, Hatori?
[Hatori] It's
all in the past.
I'm sorry...
There's nothing
to apologize for...
I do still speak with
Kana from time to time...
But that's all.
Now I wonder if you would be
so kind as to excuse me...
I believe I've said
enough for one day.
Uh? Oh, no, please...
I'd like it if you stayed...
Maybe you could give me
a tour of the house-
Hatori!?
Ahh! Water!
No- Seawater!
Which one is it!?
What do I do?! Hatori!
Hello, in there?
I'm Kana Sohma...
It's nice
to meet you.
I'll be your new
assistant, as of today.
So whatever you need me
to do, just say the word.
Aha! This is a
little strange, huh?
I guess we're part
of the same family,
and I've never even
seen you before...
But, when I told my friends
I'd be working with you,
they all warned me
you'd be handsome...
[Hatori] This will
be your desk...
And these are
today's charts...
You'll want to start
looking them over-
Ah! It's snowing! I knew
it would snow today...
Say... here's a
question for you.
When the snow melts,
what does it become?
The answer is
water, of course.
Bzz-bzz! Nope!
It becomes Spring!
I think Spring is my
favorite time of year.
[Hatori] Oftentimes, in
memory, there is a tendency
to overly romanticize
the people we care about...
I know this... And
in spite of this fact,
the truth remains-
she was my Spring.
Yes. If,
as Akito said,
I had become the frozen
snow in the dark,
secretive world
of the Sohmas...
then she was the
fresh, vibrant Spring...
full of life,
and light...
[Hatori] It seems
almost inevitable now,
the way we were
drawn to each other...
It was the beginning
of a beautiful dream.
And then...
...she
found out.
W-water! No!
Seawater! I don't know!
Which one is it!?
What do I do?! Hatori!
I will say this,
at least-
if you threw a real sea horse
into the tub like that...
it would
probably die.
I was afraid
of that.
I was so shaken up,
I couldn't think!
But, I guess I finally
know the reason...
I'd been wondering why it was
you never wanted to hold me...
It's because you were
afraid, is that it?
You were afraid of what
would happen if I found out...
That's why you keep your
distance from people...
especially the
ones you love.
But you don't have to
be afraid. Not of me.
Hatori.. I'm so glad
to have met you...
And I'm even happier to have
fallen in love with you...
I want to
stay with you.
[Hatori]
I wept.
For the first
time in my life,
I felt as though I had
been allowed something-
as though I had been
saved from something...
I could not
stop the tears-
they were the
frozen snow,
melted by the first
warm breath of Spring.
I lost myself
in the dream...
And I laughed,
as never before.
As though years of happiness
had been compressed
into each and every
new moment we shared...
[Hatori] Kana and I
wish to be married.
But all dreams
must end...
[Akito] No! I won't allow
it! I refuse to allow it!
[Akito] Hatori,
what's wrong?
[Akito]
Hatori...
You did this!
This is your fault!
If Hatori loses his
sight, it's your fault!
It's your fault!
Akito!
...Hatori!
Do you think you can lift
the Sohma curse? Do you?!
[Shigure] Kana! Hurry!
Take Hatori out of here!
Let me go! Let me go!
You can't lift the curse!
We don't need you!
You're worthless to us!
It's your fault!
It's all your
faaaaaa-ult!
[Hatori] No matter what I
said, no matter what I did,
each time I tried to console
her she collapsed into tears,
until eventually, her grief
began to consume her...
[Akito] It's especially
at times like this
that your techniques become
useful. Don't you agree?
We both know her memory
should be erased.
Before now, I doubt you
would have even hesitated.
At this very moment,
it's her memories of you,
her feelings for you...
that cause her to suffer.
You're the only one
who can save her.
You can put an end
to her suffering...
It will be your final
act of love... Hatori.
[Kana] It would
have been better...
The truth is, she wants
you to release her...
[Kana] ...better if you
and I had never met...
The truth is, she
wants to forget...
...would have been better...
if you and I had never met...
[Hatori]
In the past,
even if I knew the pain
or sadness it might cause,
it was a burden I
was forced to bear.
I had no choice but to
erase a person's memory
once the order
was given...
How could I have
known that by hand,
the person dearest to me would
also have her memories erased,
the very memories
we shared together...
This was
my reward.
Thank you, Kana. Everything
will be all right now.
You won't have to be
troubled over me any longer.
I hope that
one day,
you will meet someone who
can truly make you happy...
It is my dearest
wish that you do...
[Kana]
Hatori...
I'm so sorry... I wasn't able
to protect you... Forgive me...
[Hatori] I was the one who
should have apologized...
I was the one who
couldn't protect her...
[Kana] Hatori... I'm so
glad to have met you...
And I'm even happier to have
fallen in love with you...
[Hatori] I knew that day that I
would live the rest of my life
as the
frozen snow,
so that the dream
we had together
would never
melt away...
Sorry things
didn't work out.
But what I was able
to learn from you
will be my pride
as a doctor!
I mean as soon as
I finish school.
[Tohru]
Hatori...
Please, if there's anything
you can do to help him...
I know I'm glad to have met
the Sohmas. I don't regret it.
I can't imagine anymore
what my life would be like
without them...
You must have felt
that way once too, Kana.
So, if there's
anything you can do
to help Hatori
now, please...
Oh! I'm sorry! I
didn't look! No, I uh...
I didn't know
what else to do,
so I moved you up into the room
here where you could lay down.
And I know it's
not the best thing,
but all I had to cover
you up with was my coat.
I know it's dirty
and all, I'm...
I'm sorry, but like I
said it's all I had...
Did you
see it?
No! You see,
I uh...
I mean my
zodiac form...
Yes... I did, and I
thought it was really cute...
it was pretty amazing to
see what animal you were...
But, more
than that,
I'm really just glad
you're okay... huh?
Oh, here. I hope
you don't mind.
I sort of took
it without asking.
It's been quite some time
since I've dreamed of her...
Perhaps it's the
snow that reminds me...
[Kana] Say... here's
a question for you.
Tell me... when the snow
melts, what does it become?
Huh? Mmm,
Let's see...
It becomes
Spring, right?
So, even when
it's cold like this,
I always remember that
Spring is on its way!
It's sort of neat
to think about.
No matter how much snow there
is, it's all going to melt.
It always
does...
I think Spring is my
favorite time of year.
Oh! You must
be freezing...
Here,
take this.
Of course
Autumn's nice too.
And you couldn't have
Spring without it!
Say, if you'd
like I could go in
and try to find something
hot to warm us up!
Hm?! Something to warm us
up? Feels like, deja vu...
[Shigure] Ah! Lo and
behold, there they are!
[Tohru]
Uh? Shigure!
Well... I've been
looking for you.
Imagine my surprise, I found
a little lost bunny instead...
Momiji! Oh, I guess it wasn't
deja vu. You have drinks!
Sorry it
took so long.
Ha'ri.
So what
brings you here?
Here, Tohru!
Thank you
very much!
I suddenly had this
feeling that Tohru was here
in need of
a rescue...
Call it a writer's
intuition, if you will...
That's a lie.
You only came to see
the New Year's
preparations, didn't you?
Don't let
them fool you.
These two have been
friends since they were kids.
Oh, Tohru, have you asked Ha'ri
what zodiac animal he is?
One more
word, Shigure,
and the entire
publishing industry
will know every embarrassing
thing you've done
since you
were four...
Understood...
My lips are sealed.
It's not like it's
that hard to figure out.
[Hatori]
Momiji!
I really don't see
how it's anything
you should be
embarrassed about...
It's so warm!
I can see how today might
have been stressful for you..
But now that
it's over,
Hatori's not that
bad of a guy, is he?
No! In fact, he was
really quite the gentleman!
[Tohru] I wonder...
could that have been...?
Let's go, Tohru...
You'd better stay with me.
It's easy to
get lost in here.
Shigure, tell me...
What is the curse, exactly?
I mean, am I doing anything
that I shouldn't be?
I wouldn't worry...
Just keep being yourself.
That's really all
you need to know.
[Tohru] It's been
a strange day.
It seems like I learned a
lot, but at the same time,
it still feels like I don't
know anything at all...
[Shigure]
I'm home!
[Tohru] Me too!
We're here!
Sorry we're
so late...
Ah I guess sitting around
the heater like that
got to be a little
bit too comfortable...
I guess so.
It might be dangerous to
try and wake them up.
Why don't we let them
sleep for a while...
[Tohru] At any rate...
I do know one thing...
I know I'm going to
try to always remember
the way I feel
right now...
About everyone,
about living here--
I never want those
feelings to change.
Every day that I live in
this house is dear to me.
Every single day...
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
[Yuki] So, Miss Honda,
what are you going to make?
[Tohru] New
Year's cakes!
[Yuki] Uh? New
Year's cakes?
[Tohru]
Uh-huh!
I just hope I picked out
ingredients everyone likes...
[Yuki] Shigure, Kyo, and
I will be going back
to the main house
tonight... I'm sorry...
[Tohru]
That's all right...
[Shigure] Okay, it's
almost time to go..
Don't you think you two
ought to get ready?
[Yuki &amp; Kyo]
I'm not going.
[Tohru] Promise,
I'll be fine...
And I'll take great care of
the house while you're gone...
You are talking to
the girl who-Aah!
The bathwater! I left
it running again!
[Shigure] If that doesn't
inspire confidence,
nothing will.