I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
Look at that beautiful sky!
See you later, Mom! Take care of
the house while I'm gone, okay?
I'll be back!
Hello! My name is Tohru Honda. I
haven't always lived in a tent.
Up until last May,
I lived with my Mom.
It was just the two of us.
But then the accident...
After I lost Mom, I began
secretly living here, on my own.
It's not exactly
comfortable, but it's alright.
And it's what I have to do.
Like my motto says:
"Never give up!"
Look at this, Mom. Did you
know there was a house here?
It seems so peaceful.
Must be nice.
How cute! The twelve
animals of the Zodiac!
My word...
Do my eyes deceive me,
or is there a strange young
girl standing on my porch?
Ah, I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
I was just looking!
I didn't mean to barge
in without permission.
It's all right...
I'd just set them out
to dry... No harm done.
But, I find it hard
to believe that
these silly little things
could attract your interest...
No, I really like them. I don't
think they're silly at all!
Yes, well... I must admit,
I'm particularly
fond of them myself.
Oh. But I should have known...
You left out the cat.
The cat?  Ahhh...
I take it you're referring
to the old folktale
of the Chinese Zodiac?
Uh huh... My mom told it
to me when I was little.
A long, long time ago,
God decided to invite all
of the animals to a banquet...
He sent out word
for all of them
to come to his house
the following evening...
"and don't be late!" he said.
When the mischievous
rat heard the news,
he decided to play a trick
on his neighbor, the cat.
He told the cat that the party
was the day after tomorrow.
The very next day,
all of the animals lined
up for the celebration.
And the rat led the way,
riding all the way there
on the back of the cow.
Everyone had a wonderful time.
Except for the foolish cat.
Who missed the whole thing.
Hey, why are you crying?
Because... that poor cat...
he must be so lonely.
I know, I won't be a dog
anymore! I'll be a cat, too!
Funny... I wonder what he'll
say when he hears he has a fan.
H-He?
You were born in
the Year of the Dog?
I knew there was
something I liked about you,
aside from your pretty fa--
Please forgive my
cousin, Miss Honda.
He's a bit of a flirt,
but he's harmless...
In general, it's usually
best to just ignore him.
Ah, Yuki Sohma!
Oh, Mom, I don't believe it!
The prince of my high school,
Yuki Sohma is standing right
here, before my very eyes!
And I'm standing
in front of his house!
A dictionary?
No. I have two of them.
So- you're one of
Yuki's classmates from school.
Let's start again.
I'm Shigure,
his older and much
less violent cousin.
Hi, it's very nice to meet you!
And what brings you to our
home this morning, Miss Honda?
Well, you know I live...
nearby...
You do? Where at?
Uhh, right!
Okay, I think I'll just be going
now. It was nice to meet you-
Wait, Miss Honda!
Since you're here, why
don't we walk together?
L - O - V - E!
We- love- Yu-ki!
Yuki! Yuki!
Yuki?!
Okay. Start Talking.
What was that all
about, Miss Tohru?
Why were you walking to
school with Prince Yuki?
Details!
And they better be good.
It... It was just
a coincidence...
Well for your sake,
I hope that's all it was!
Every girl at Kaiwaia
High, Class 1-D knows
Yuki Sohma's the best
looking boy in school!
And he's intelligent!
And great at sports!
And for your info we are
the Prince Yuki Fan Club!
We've got first dibs, sister,
so you better stay clear!
Hey!
What?!
She said it was a coincidence.
Now get lost... before those big
noses of yours get bruised...
Now, hold it, Yankee!
You're not gonna scare us
with that 'street thug' talk!
One more word,
and you'll all get...
[Beep]
...with electric shocks.
Thanks, I didn't
think they'd ever leave!
Were those catty little
girls bothering you? Aww.
Hana, don't actually
shock anyone, okay?
You know the truth is,
I was so nervous walking
with Yuki this morning.
I couldn't talk to him-
no, I couldn't even look at him.
I sense strange electric
signals coming from that boy.
Here we go again,
Hana's Electric Report.
Strange how?
I don't know. He's different.
Well, I admit
he does seem to have an
air of mystery about him...
And there are some weird
stories floating around, too...
I hear one of those Fan Club
girls tried to ask him out once,
but he just pushed her away...
And I mean that literally.
Right in the hall.
Then he left her on
the floor and ran off.
Like I said, I sense
strange electric signals.
Let's talk about something else?
How's that job of yours going?
Oh, fine I guess. Why?
I don't know...
You've been putting
in a lot of hours lately.
A lot more than usual.
Uhh... Yeah. Sure.
You're having trouble saving
up for your tuition, aren't you?
No it's just... well... yeah.
That's odd... I didn't think
tuition here was that expensive.
And I don't remember you
having to work this hard before.
Unless, something
else has changed?
No... everything's the sa--
So what is it? You in some kind
of trouble? You owe somebody?
Your grandfather's giving
you enough to eat, right?
He isn't taking your money?
Mm, mm!
I know, I worry too much...
But seriously, if you need me
to rough someone up for you,
you just say the word. Got it?
Okay.
Uo's going to kill me
when she finds out...
But how can I tell my two best
friends that I live in a tent?
I can still remember how tough
it was on Mom after Dad died.
She had to work so hard
just to make ends meet.
But she never
seemed to mind.
She always had a smile!
It's hard to believe that
someone so smart and so strong
could be taken away
by an accident...
After it happened,
there were a lot of people I
could have stayed with, I guess.
I chose to live with
my paternal grandfather.
He was always so nice to me.
But he's retired now,
and living on his savings.
I didn't want to be a burden,
so I promised him I would work
to pay for my tuition myself!
After four months...
The house needed some
renovations, and Grandfather
went to stay with his
daughter and her family
until the work was done.
He asked me if I had a
friend here I could stay with.
I told him yes, but Uo lives
in a one-room apartment,
and Hana's got
such a large family...
I couldn't ask them.
They've got enough
to worry about.
I'd just be in the way...
That's when it hit me!
If I could somehow live
on my own for a while,
then everyone would be happy!
Oh! Yuki! It's you!
I mean, it's... Hi.
It seems we're beginning
to make a habit
of bumping into each other.
It was nice meeting your cousin
this morning. He was funny.
And those little
Zodiac figurines
he made were really cute...
Ah, yes... but I thought I
overheard you saying something
about how you wished there
was a Year of the Cat?
It's an idea I had when
I was a kid... Silly.
Cats... useless,
foolish creatures.
Tell me, Miss Honda.
How familiar would
you say you are
with the history of
the Chinese Zodiac?
I know the stories
my mom used to tell me...
Did you know that
it was originally
nothing more than
a simple calendar?
A mathematical system
to mark the passage of time.
Only later did people begin
to use it for things like
astrology and fortune-telling...
Oh. I guess the story about
the animals isn't true then...
No... I'm not really sure how
or when the animals first
came to represent the years.
But I don't believe they
were there from the beginning.
What I do know is at no time
in the history of the Zodiac
has the cat ever been included.
So you see, the cat has
been shunned by society
for thousands of years.
But as the story is told, it
still yearns to be accepted...
Like I say,
a truly foolish animal.
Sounds like you
really don't like cats.
I noticed it this morning
that you're starting
to look a bit pale...
You should try to take
better care of yourself.
Perhaps we'll bump into
each other again tomorrow...
Wow... He really is mysterious!
But I'll pretend I didn't
hear that "pale" remark!
I can't afford to let
anything bring me down!
I've got too much to do!
Besides, Mom probably
had it much, much worse.
Wha--? Hey, you gonna let
this trash sit here all night?
Oh! Sorry!
Like my motto says,
"Never give up, no matter
what life throws your way!"
Whew. If we keep eating
out like this all the time,
I'm going to have
to buy a bigger robe.
Well, then why don't
you do the cooking.
Why? Every time I
make dinner you complain.
Pickled radish and curry is
not dinner. It's disgusting.
I think one complaint
is more or less justified.
You know Yuki, you've got a
good head on your shoulders,
but I just don't think you're
cut out for housework.
Let's get a housekeeper?
No.
Hold up...
Miss Honda?
Hi, Mom. I'm home.
I know... It's late.
But I can't sleep yet.
I still have a paper to write.
I'm just going to go
down to the stream
and wash up a little, okay?
Shigure, don't you think
you're overdoing it?
So... You've been living
in that tent by yourself?
Uh, huh.
For how long?
I don't know. Just over a week?
Well, that explains it. All of
this land is Sohma property.
It seemed odd that we'd
suddenly have a new neighbor...
I'm sorry... But please...
Can't I stay there
a little while longer?
It's only for a few
more weeks, then I'll go!
I don't have much money,
but I can pay you!
Please let me stay?
Those woods aren't too safe...
You've got wild
animals, landslides,
the occasional
weirdo prowling around.
It's not a good idea for a girl
to be living out there alone.
So you're done laughing?
Don't you worry about me! I'm
already used to all the bugs!
And if I can stand up to
them, I can stand up to...
Miss Tohru!
A fever.
Ice! I'll get ice! It's uh-
It's...
And you call the woods unsafe?
Well, relatively speaking.
There. You hear that?
There's just been another
landslide somewhere.
Really? But how
do you know that?
I guess you could
say it's instinct.
Was it close?
Close to the tent-er,
I mean-- Not at all!
Oh! This is terrible! Mom's
picture was still in there!
I've got to get her out! Mom!
Mom! I'm coming!
Please, calm down.
You already have a fever.
But, Mom...
Wh-What am I going to do?
If I don't get her out soon...
sh-she'll be hurt!
Don't strain yourself. We'll
come back when it's brighter...
I think your Mom's probably
glad it wasn't you in there.
And I think she'd be upset if
you got hurt now... Don't you?
There. Isn't that better?
And Yuki's still looking for
some ice, if you want it...
I'm sorry...
You must be tired. It's a
lot to happen in one day...
I... I lost my home again...
Are you okay?
Yes... It's sad... but,
not as sad as other things...
Like what?
Like... not telling Mom
"be safe" on the day she died...
I said that every morning...
Bye. Be safe. Except
that day. I didn't say it...
I had a test. So I stayed up
studying almost the whole night.
When it was time for Mom to
go to work, I didn't wake up.
I couldn't tell her "be safe".
And she never came home...
I used to think about
quitting school... working.
Mom told me she
didn't finish school.
But she always
wished that she did.
That's why I need
you to stick with it.
So you can tell me
what it feels like
to hold that
diploma in your hand.
And then, maybe, you can have
the life I never got to have...
When she said that,
that's when I knew...
Why she worked so hard...
It was all for me.
And with everything she did,
I couldn't even get up
long enough to say "goodbye"
when she was
walking out the door.
Not even that one little thing.
And then she was gone...
So now, I have
to finish high school
like Mom wanted me to,
no matter what...
I have to hold that
diploma in my hand...
I have to... for her...
I can't give up...
just because...
of a fever... like this...
It's amazing...
She always seems
so cheerful at school...
You'd never guess
she's been suffering
like this for so long...
When I was young,
there were many times I wanted
to run away from Sohma House...
But I never did.
I could always find some
rationalization to stay...
The fact of the matter is,
I just wasn't strong enough,
or I could've left...
I could've lived in the
woods by myself, in a tent...
I could've done what she did...
You can call it amazing...
But I don't think the
word does it justice...
No... No, it doesn't.
Do you mind
keeping an eye on her?
I'd like to go out for a while.
What? Where? You're not going
to try digging out that tent--?
You are. Aren't you?
Do you want me
to come with you?
It won't be an easy
job for you alone...
You're right...
but I don't think I said
that I was going alone...
Be safe, Yuki.
Tohru... Tohru...?
You've got a fever again.
You don't have to push
yourself so hard...
You don't have to do
things the way I did.
You can just be yourself.
Do things your own way,
one step at a time.
You'll get there...
I promise...
Mom?
Just be yourself.
You'll be fine...
Mom, you're here...
But how did you--?
Good morning!
How are you feeling today?
Um, I, guess I, uhh...
I've brought your
things for you.
I think this is all of them,
if you'd like to check.
Yuki, this must have
taken you all night!
Don't be silly.
So, then how did you-?
I mean, there was so much...
It's a secret.
Oh...
I know the place is dirty...
What?
And I realize the idea of
living with two strange boys
might seem a little awkward...
But there's an
extra room upstairs.
You're welcome to stay
there if you'd like.
No, no, no! Out of the question!
We're not that strange...
No! I didn't mean it like that!
Of course, it won't be free...
I do intend to pay
you for your services.
For my... services?
♪ As our brand new
housekeeper! ♪
We'll just take your
things to your room now.
I assume your references
will all check out?
Wait! I can't let you do this!
Not after all the trouble
you've gone through already!
Please, it's too much!
Miss Honda, we're doing
this because we want to.
You don't have to worry that
it's causing us any trouble...
And besides...
Where else can you go?
Oh...
Well, if I'm going
to stay here,
I'll work for room and
board, and that's it!
I don't want any money!
And I want to know all
the rules of the house!
Relax. It's all right.
You can do things
your own way here.
The only thing you have to do
is be yourself... Fair enough?
Just be yourself...
You'll be fine...
I don't know. Do you
really think it's a good idea
having a girl in the house?
Naturally. Now it occurs to
you to worry... But I wouldn't.
We'll be okay, as long as
she doesn't try to hug us...
All's well that ends well,
I guess...
But I'm still not sure how
I ended up in Yuki's house.
or borrowing
some of his clothes...
It's like being in a dream...
I apologize for the smell.
We've had this room
closed off for some time...
it's probably best to keep the
windows open for a while...
Yo.
Time to pay the piper,
rat-boy. I'm here to collect.
Funny. I would have thought
he'd send somebody bigger.
That's right.
You better get your tough talk
out of the way while you can,
'cause I'm about to wipe
that stupid little smirk
right off of your face!
Wait! Stop! Don't fight!
Yuki, what were all those
crashing sounds I just heard?
Kyo's not here, is he?
I'm so sorry!
Are you all right? I--
Ah! I turned him
into a cat! I'm so sorry!
--Hold on...
--I don't know how it happened!
But we're going
to help you, okay?
Hurry! We have to get him
to a doctor, right away!
--Miss Honda!
--Tohru!
Oh Mom, I think this
must all be a dream!
Everybody's
turning into animals!
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
Tohru, I'm a dog. Yuki
here is a rat. That's Kyo.
Don't let his temper scare you.
He's got a bit of a
chip on his shoulder.
Your planing on erasing Miss
Honda's memories, aren't you?
Just like in the old days.
I believe I will
trust Miss Honda.
For Yuki, and for Kyo.
Even for myself.
This may be
a great opportunity.
What I was thinking. I don't
even know where to start.
But, Tohru Honda
never gives up!