I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
Hi, it's
me, Tohru.
I guess even before
I got to know him,
I always thought of
Yuki as a prince.
He always seemed so
perfect at school.
But now I know that there's
another side to him--
a shy, awkward side that he
doesn't like people to see.
Of course, he's still pretty
mysterious in a lot of ways,
but the fact that he's
allowed me to see him more
for who he
really is, well-
now I can say, more than
ever, he truly is a prince.
[Motoko] I love Yuki.
I love his
beautiful silver hair,
and the way it sparkles
in the sunlight,
his creamy
white skin,
the way his luscious
lashes caress his cheeks
when his eyes
are closed,
his sweet,
sweet voice.
I love everything.
Yuki is my everything!
L-O-V-E! We love Yuki! Yuki!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la!
[Motoko] Prince Yuki Fan
Club Vice-President,
Minami
Kinoshita!
Right!
Member Number 1,
Mio Yamagishi!
That's me!
Member Number 2,
Mai Gotou!
Here!
And I am the President of
the Prince Yuki Fan Club,
Motoko
Minagawa!
Together - we
shall prevail!
[All] We shall
prevail!
And with
hands united...
[All] With
hands united!
We will do everything
in our power to protect
our beloved prince
and keep him safe!
We will keep
him safe!
Repeat: "Do not touch
the Prince's belongings."
[All] Do not touch the
Prince's belongings!
Repeat: "Do not enter
the Prince's house."
[All] Do not enter
the Princes' house!
Repeat: "Do not
speak to the Prince
unless accompanied by at
least two other members!"
[All] Do not speak
to the Prince
unless accompanied by at
least two other members!
When speaking to the Prince,
address him as follows.
Third Years: "Yuki".
"Yuki".
Second Years:
"Prince Yuki".
First Years:
"Prince Yuki Sohma".
"Prince
Yuki Sohma".
Hail to
the Prince.
[All] Hail to
the Prince!
You guys again?
Go home, already.
Today I'm
not leaving
until those tight lips of yours
come unsealed. Got it Makoto?
I want you to give me the
names of the students
who will be assisting Yuki on
the student council next year.
Ah, yes, "Prince Yuki". You're
a very determined girl, Motoko,
but you can't always get
what you want, now can you?
And I will not give out
privileged information
simply because
you want it
to fulfill your own
personal agenda.
Oh, taking the
high road are we?
Or could it be that our current
student council president
is so incompetent he
still hasn't finalized
next year's
roster?
Those weird "Prince Yuki Fan
Club" girls are back again.
Why are they so worried
about next year's members?
They're the Prince Yuki
Fan Club. It's what they do.
I don't even need
the entire list!
All I need to know is whether
or not there will be any girls
on the new
student council!
Just give us
those names,
and you can keep the rest of
your "privileged information"!
Hmmm!
Oh, now I
get it.
I can't tell you how important
this is. We just have to know!
Oh, come
on, Yuki.
We don't want some
evil temptress
trying to steal our
beloved Yuki's heart!
I tell
you now,
if you try to put a girl
like that on the council,
we will not let you
get away with it!
Mm-hm!
My task is to
select a council
that will support
Yuki as president.
I will choose the best
students for the job,
regardless of gender.
To that end...
Even if it means
repeating a year,
should the need arise,
I, Takei Makoto,
will make
that sacrifice
and offer
my own hand
in support of our
glorious president Yuki!
And I would also hold
myself back a year
so that I could graduate
with my sweet Yuki,
and we could share
the next four years
of university
together!
That's ridiculous! Why would
you do a thing like that?!
Well,
excuse me!
You're the one
who brought it up!
Look at
'em go.
Two-to-one they both
miss graduation
'cause they're still having
this stupid argument.
This stinks. How many
times do we gotta ask
before President Takei
gives us the stupid list?
He probably wants to
keep it under wraps
until he can make the
formal announcement.
So why don't we try sneaking
into the Student Council Office
when he's
not there?
I'm afraid it may
just come to that.
Still, this
worries me.
The fact that Takei
won't give us the names-
doesn't that prove already
that there is a girl
on the new
student council?
Oh, um, by the way,
President Motoko?
And I just know she's
going to be some catty,
calculating,
little witch!
Oh! My Yuki
is in danger!
President
Motoko!
Shouldn't we start thinking
about who we're gonna pick
to be the next Prince Yuki
Fan Club' President soon?
I mean, seeing as how you're
graduating this year and all.
That's right! Only
half a year left to go!
Yeah,
congratulations!
Of course, I think it
goes without saying
that the best choice for
our next President is me,
Minami
Kinosh- aagh!
Uh-uh! It's me!
Mio Yamagish- aagh!
No! Minami
Kinoshita!
She's a girl that knows
how to get things done!
How's that for
getting things done?!
I think I want to be
the new vice-president!
What do you mean? Why don't
you wanna be the President?
Oh, well the Vice-President
doesn't have to do any work!
Then that
settles it!
I'm the next President,
and you're my new V.P.!
Shut up! You don't just
get to decide on your own!
Well I just
did, so there!
I outrank you,
you know!
Y-Yes,
you're right.
We'll start thinking
about this very soon.
Uh, hey
wait up.
It's
Yuki!
But he's with
Tohru Honda again!
I'm so mad! What's so great
about that stupid Tohru Honda?!
Nothing! There's not a
single good thing about her!
Seriously, I know the student
council thing is a problem,
but I think this one's gotta
be a million times worse!
President Motoko! We
have to do something!
We've gotta teach
that girl a lesson!
Yeah, we've gotta
do something!
And fast, too!
Before it's too late!
I don't know.
Yes, you're right.
I think it's time we put an
end to this, once and for all.
Personally, I've never
been zapped before,
and I'd really like
to keep it that way.
So there is no way I'm
messing with Tohru
as long as that
Electric Girl's around!
Hey! Wait
for me!
What's on your
mind, Hana?
Just waving hello
to someone.
"Graduation"... Never has
there been so much sadness
in a single word.
Sweet Yuki...
It's true. Because when the
Spring comes, I will graduate.
Then there will be no
more stealing glances
at your perfect face,
like the one I had today.
No more
talking with you.
I still haven't
forgotten, Yuki.
That beautiful day--
the day I talked to you for
the first time, that moment.
Yuki? Hi.
Yes, that single,
perfect moment
was more
precious to me
than all the greatest
treasures of the world,
priceless and
irreplaceable.
I just wanted to tell you, I
think you're really beautiful.
Thank you. That's very
kind of you to say.
Ever since that day, I
have been a slave to love.
And my small,
pitiful heart,
it has been filled
to the breaking point
with my
love of you.
Yuki...
Ahh, Yuki! It is my fate to
be forever cursed and blessed
by visions of
your angelic face!
Like a prick upon the thorn
of a rose, your love--
For the love of--!
Keep it down, Motoko!
You're waking
the neighbors!
Mother! Haven't you
ever heard of knocking!
Sure! "Knock!
Knock! Knock!
Can I come in,
Princess Loudmouth?!"
Now enough with this silly
crush of yours. Go to bed!
It wouldn't
be like this
if I hadn't been born
a year too early!
What?! What in the world
are you babbling about now?
It's your fault. It's your
fault! It's all your fault!
Oh, what is wrong with you?
Cut it out, will you?
And what's this?
Another love poem?!
Why are you wasting all your
time on these useless things?
Go sell a radish
or something!
Earn your keep!
I'm not selling
any radishes!
I know! That's the problem!
We own a vegetable store!
Yes, and
being born here
was the worst thing that
ever happened to me!
Bite your tongue!
That store downstairs
pays for this roof
over your head,
not to mention all this paper
you waste on your love poems!
[Neighbor] The Minagawas
are at it again.
Yeah, like
they ever stop.
just so we can put food in
your ungrateful little...
For the last time, I'm
not going to tell you!
Gah. He really
is a tight-ass.
So, it has
come to this.
We have no choice but
to use our last resort.
We must infiltrate the
Student Council Office!
Ahh, I get it. So that's
why you called me.
Will you
help me,
Prince Yuki Fan Club
Senior Member, Rika Aida?
You know I will. There's not
much I wouldn't do for Yuki.
I'll get you
in that room.
Don't worry. They haven't
made the lock yet
that Rika Aida
can't open.
Yes, your talent is an
inspiration to us all.
Isn't that
right, everyone?
I didn't even know Rika
could do this sort of thing.
It's pretty shady.
I hope she's not
turning out to be
some kinda' crook
or something.
What is she thinking, letting
a skill like that go to waste?!
We could totally sneak
into Yuki's house!
We should try to get
our hands on a map
of the Student
Council Office.
You know, like a
blueprint or something.
It'll help to know how
it's laid out on the inside.
Yes, good thinking! After
all, it pays to be prepared!
Let's look around and
see what we can dig up.
...Or maybe, even
having a dream,
where he turns a
little bit in bed...
Maybe this is taking
it a little too far.
I was worried
before, but this.
Isn't this like a
crime, or something?
No... This is...
This is love!
But I'm pretty sure
it's still a crime.
My sweet Yuki,
can't you see?
There's nothing I
won't do for you.
I'll go to any lengths
to protect you,
even if I have
to stoop so low
as to resort to sneaking
around like this.
No. There's nothing
"low" about it.
There's no shame in
what I'm doing.
It's what has to be
done. Because for me...
"Records Room"
Somehow, I don't
think we're gonna find
any blueprints
in here.
Maybe not. But maybe we'll
find something else we can use.
At any rate, as
long as we're here
we should at
least take a look.
...because
for me,
Yuki is more important
than anything-- everything!
And compared to him,
nothing else matters.
Nothing... Not
even my own life.
Y- Yuki...
Yuki!
Hey! What a coincidence!
What are you doing here?
Uh, well, I've been asked
to plan the schedule
for the
class trip.
It's Yuki!
It's really Yuki!
Right here! Right
before my eyes!
...schedules from
previous trips.
Anyway, it's been a long
time, hasn't it, Miss Aida?
You too,
Miss Minagawa.
And it has
been so long,
since I've talked to
him, face to face.
Oh! So then would you like to
hear what we did on our trip?
I mean, if you
think it would help,
we'd be glad to tell
you. Won't we Motoko?
Oh... uh...
uh-huh...
I have to make the most of
this chance fate has given me.
I have to try to talk to him,
for as long as possible!
Yes, that would be helpful.
Thank you very much.
This is it! Right now,
I have to say something.
I have to find a way
to tell him how I feel.
But I can't say anything
to scare him away.
I have to say something
to grab his attention,
something interesting,
and intelligent.
The countdown to
graduation has begun,
and now I've been
given this one chance.
I can't
mess this up!
Yu- Yu-
Y-Y- Yuki?
You're so--
I mean I--
I mean what did you
have for breakfast?
What did I have
for... breakfast?
I messed
it up.
Ah, well, when
you're on a trip,
it's really important
to start the day
with a nice,
healthy breakfast.
You know, so you have plenty
of energy and everything.
Breakfast.
Well, let's see.
Today I had rice, and
miso soup, some fish stew.
Oh, and leek
porridge.
The Prince
eats...
...leek
porridge?
That doesn't sound like
a very good breakfast.
W-well, I think
it's very sensible!
Say what you will, but leeks
are really very nutritious.
They're loaded with
health benefits,
not to mention the wonders
they do for the complexion!
And actually, steamed
leeks can be quite tasty!
Ah, yes, I like
those too.
I don't believe it!
Yuki just smiled at me!
Miss Minagawa?
Ah, the sight
of that smile
is like a million
volts down my spine!
And what's more-- we
both like steamed leeks!
It's as though we were
destined to be together!
Miss Minagawa...
I'm wondering, is this
something you do often?
Huh?
That is, do you always talk
to yourself like this?
Oh well, yes, I--
I guess I do,
I mean it depends.
Why do you ask?
Oh, no
reason.
Ah! I'm sorry! It's
annoying, isn't it?!
You think I'm
annoying!
Oh, no, I didn't
mean it like that.
I just, I think
it's cute, is all.
Uh! C'mon Motoko, what are you
doing? He said it was cute!
No, he wasn't
talking about me.
And it's not me that he's
smiling at. I know that much.
I'm not the one who's given him
reason to smile so tenderly,
in a way he was
never able to before.
But what, then?
What is the reason?
In the year and a half
that I've loved him,
I've followed his every
move, his every breath.
But what I couldn't see,
somewhere deep inside,
in some place my
eyes couldn't reach--
...he's
changed.
Without my even
realizing it, he's changed.
Is this the way it's
going to be from now on?
Is he going to continue to
change in ways I can't see?
In ways that
I won't know,
because he's together
with someone else.
Is it that someone
who's changing him?
Stop.
Stop, get
away from him!
You can't have him!
Don't get any closer!
Get your hands
off of him!
I'm, uh-- I don't know
what I-- I mean-- I just--
Excuse me, I think I need
to go freshen up a bit.
Hold on! Motoko,
wait a second!
This is
the worst.
This is the worst thing
that could've happened!
That's it. It's over.
Everything, it's finished now.
To do something like
that, in front of Yuki,
how can I ever
look at him again?
How, after I've shown
him such an ugly face?
But I know what he
saw was the real me.
I can't stand any other
girl getting close to him.
Whether it's
Tohru Honda,
or the girl who might
join the student council,
or the new fan
club president.
How can I ever choose another
girl to take my place?
I hate them all!
All of them!
They're enemies,
every single one!
But really, the one
I hate the most...
It's myself, the
hideous, ugly "me"
that thinks these
horrible thoughts.
All of those
other stupid,
calculating,
self-centered girls,
if I hate them, it's
because in them
I only see the things
I hate about myself.
Miss Minagawa?
Oh, Yuki! It's you! W-what
are you doing here?
I wanted to apologize. I mean,
if I said something back there
that hurt your
feelings.
Oh! No, no not at
all! Absolutely not!
You don't have to
apologize for anything.
B-but still, I'm honored
that someone as cool as you
would worry
about me.
Well, I... I don't know
if I'd say I'm cool.
I say and do some pretty
awkward things sometimes, too.
Yuki...
He has to know that I
adore him so completely.
have so much love for him
that my heart
could burst.
Yes, I think he
must know. And now,
even though I let him see
such an ugly side of myself,
even though I'm the one
who acted like a fool,
he's here, trying
to comfort me.
So do--
So do I.
Sometimes I say
awkward things too.
The truth is I didn't
want to see it.
I didn't want to see
him changed like this.
I didn't want to know that
there was a place in his heart
I could
never reach.
Not when knowing hurts
so much. And yet.
And yet, I--
Seeing Yuki here, smiling like
this, it makes me so happy.
And I never want
him to stop smiling.
Even though I know that he's
not smiling because of me,
as much as that
hurts to admit.
What a sweet, sorrowful
thing love can be.
This mad, crazy,
out-of-control love.
And the things
it's made me do,
some of the awful,
shameful, things.
I don't deserve to love
someone like him. But still--
Motoko!
Time hasn't run
out completely.
And maybe, I'll do
some changing, too.
Maybe grow up a
little. And then...
And then something
amazing might happen.
So it's
settled!
As long as there's hope,
I am not going to give up!
My love is for
one, and one alone.
Sweet, sweet, Yuki, you
will always be my prince.
I know this now, more
than ever before.
And I will never give up!
I shall prevail!
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
[Ritsu] Oh no! My
bag! My bag is torn!
I am so,
so sorry.
I can't seem to go anywhere
without causing problems
for everyone
around me.
I'm just a born
troublemaker, I suppose.
I don't deserve to
share the same air
with the rest of
the human race.
Aaah! I'm sorry! I
apologize to the world,
to the whole
universe!
I'm sorry I came
here today!
[Tohru] Um, are
you... Are you Ritsu?
I'm sorry! I'm not keeping
you from anything, am I?