I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
[Tohru]
Here you go.
All right!
Here's an idea-
what do you say we go
on a trip tomorrow?
Huh?
After all, this
is Golden Week.
It would be a shame if we
didn't do something special...
Chances like this
don't come very often.
What kinda' crazy talk are
you spewing over there?
You drunk
or somethin'?
No, but even if I
had been drinking,
it wouldn't
affect me...
Only because you always
seem like you're drunk...
At any rate... I
thought we might go
to one of the
Sohma spas,
or perhaps the lake house...
How does that sound, Tohru?
But I've already been given
a trip to the hot springs!
I couldn't go on another
one! It would be too much!
And what a lovely trip
that must have been.
It's too bad I wasn't
able to be there...
I did so, want to
go... but now...
I guess I'll never get
to take a trip with you...
Okay, I'll go!
Have you
no shame?!
Not really...
Anyway, I assume the two
of you will want to come?
You wouldn't make
me and Tohru
spend all of that time
by ourselves, would you?
Of course, if we have to go
alone... that's fine with me...
Good, so now that
that's settled,
I thought it might be
fun to travel by car...
Don't worry, leave
all the driving to me.
Shigure... do you
even have a license?
Of course I have
a license...
Why'd you have to
think about it?!
[Tohru] And so, we
all decided to go!
The next morning, we
piled into the car
and headed out to
the Sohma's lake house!
Hatori did
the driving!
Wow... Just look
at that lake!
It's beautiful!
And big, too!
I don't know that it's
really that impressive...
Oh well... this
is the first time
I've ever really
been to a lake.
Just be careful 'Jason' doesn't
get you while you're here...
Don't even start
with your nonsense...
I'm sorry... Did
you say "Jason"?
Jason... Jason... Why does
that name sound familiar?
Jason is a giant bear they
say lives by the lake...
You don't know
much, do you...
Shut up! I
knew that!
No you
didn't.
Oh, so what kind
of a bear is he?
Why are we even
talkin' about this?
You didn't bring us
all the way here
to tell us about a
bear, did you?
Yes, why did you
bring us here?
I suddenly get the feeling
you're up to something...
Ah, you two... always
so suspicious...
All I wanted was for
everyone to come have a nice,
relaxing time
at the lake...
And you think I'm
up to something...
Instead of standing around
sniffing out conspiracies,
why don't you
try to find
a more productive
use for your time.
Oh, say... like taking
Tohru for a walk.
Oh-h... Why the
long faces, you two?
Is a walk so
terrible?
Oh, it's okay. I really
don't mind going by myself...
You know... it's just
too tense in here...
We could use someone to
come lighten the mood...
I know, I'll
call Aya!
If you do
that...
...I'll make you
eat that phone.
Take your time...
Well, suddenly it's much less
stuffy in here, don't ya think?
Shigure...
Tell me. What's
the real reason
you wanted to
come on this trip?
I don't suppose you're trying
to avoid your editor again?
Dear Mii... I
am on vacation.
Please, don't
try to find me.
AHHHHH SHIGURE!!!!!
Trying to avoid her? Don't
be silly. I left her a note.
I don't understand why
she puts up with you.
Yuki and Kyo really
do seem tense...
but they haven't even
been fighting today...
Oh no. I hope it's not because
of something I've done!
But... but what
could it have been?
Maybe it was when we
visited Mom's grave...
Maybe I did
something,
or said something to make
them uncomfortable...
And they're just not
saying anything,
because they don't want
to hurt my feelings...
Oh, uh...
I- I'm
very sorry!
I don't really know
what happened, but...
but if there's
something I said,
or something I did
to make you upset...
please, just tell
me what it is!
Really, it's
okay if you do!
Miss Honda... What brought
this on all of a sudden?
Yeah, really... What the
heck are you talking about--
Ah-hh, Kyo! Kyo,
are you okay?
Dammit! I'm fine, I
just stepped in a hole.
That looks like...
a pawprint...
It's Jason!
Jason?!
Where?!
It's not
Jason.
This is terrible! It's
dangerous! We have to go back!
We have to go back now! It's
not safe here! Come on--
Eh?
Miss Honda!
Hey,
watch out!
Everything's
going to be okay...
I've already completed
the manuscript...
I was just
teasing you.
Shigure!...
wahdayaba...
Yes, yes. I
understand... Take care.
There, I called her... I called
my editor. I hope you're happy.
Yes, I am...
Stop crying.
How can I? You
spoiled all my fun!
You call yourself
an adult.
I'm sorry... I'm
sorry! I am so sorry!
[Yuki] Miss Honda,
are you hurt at all?
No... but
I'm sorry...
[Kyo] Yeah... well just watch
where you step next time.
I know, I know... uh,
I'll go get your clothes.
I'll be
right back...
Miss Honda!
Hey, watch out!
"Watch where you step". Oh,
that's very good advice,
coming from the one
who tripped first Moron.
Hey! Like you're
one to talk!
We wouldn't be in this mess if
you hadn't gotten in my way!
The only reason
I transformed
is 'cause I tripped
over your clumsy ass!
Clumsy? You're the
one who trained
all that time in
the mountains,
and you can't even
walk down a path...
I can too! I survived
out here for four months!
You wouldn't last two days!
You're on my turf now!
So shut up and pay attention,
you might learn somethin'!
[Yuki] What can I learn
from a stupid cat like you?
You didn't even know that
Jason isn't really a bear!
He's a character
in a horror film!
Yeah? So what
if I didn't!
Like I'd waste my time watchin'
some dumb movie about a bear!
You truly are
an idiot.
Okay,
that's it!
Today's the day, rat boy! Once
I get up there, you are dead!
[Yuki] Oh, good. I haven't
heard that line in a while.
If you're
so tough,
why don't you come down
here and fight! You coward!
[Yuki] What's your hurry?
Afraid you won't be able
to beat me once
we change back?
Look at you!
Callin' all your little
rat friends to help, huh?!
You know I didn't
call them...
They just decided to
come out on their own...
But I don't see any
cats coming to help you.
I guess you have no
friends here, either...
[Kyo] Who cares?! I'll take
you all on by myself! Come on!
I'm sorry... it's just...
the way you're fighting.
Miss Honda...
Wh- what's
goin' on?
I'm sorry for
laughing...
I mean, there's really
nothing funny about fighting,
but for
some reason...
I was watching you two, and
I just couldn't help myself...
It just
hit me.
"Aww, they're back to
their old selves again."
And as soon as I thought
that, I felt so relieved...
Pretty silly,
huh...?
Miss Honda,
listen...
About what you were saying
earlier, before we all fell...
I'm not angry with you. I'm
sorry if I seemed upset...
I just had a lot
on my mind is all.
But really, it had
nothing to do with you.
I don't usually like
to let people see me
that way, but
around you,
I've gotten to feel
so comfortable,
I guess I let
my guard down...
I didn't even realize
I'd done it...
If anything, it's a sign of how
much I've come to like you.
Oh, you don't
have to--
But, I hope everything's
all right now, Miss Honda...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry
I made you worry.
Yeah, same
here...
I wasn't mad at you
either... I guess...
I guess I just had a lot of
other stuff on my mind too...
...small mind
that it is...
You damn
rat!
Um, you know... I
should apologize...
I guess I
sort of...
made a really big deal
out of nothing, didn't I?
But in a
strange way,
I'm glad that all of this
happened the way it did...
Um- not to
say I'm glad
if you were feeling upset
or anything... it's just
I'm just
glad to know
that you're comfortable
enough around me,
you don't feel you
have to hide it
it there's something on your
mind that's bothering you...
It's okay for you to let your
guard down when we're together,
if you want...
And I promise,
the next time it looks
like you're upset,
I won't say a
word about it!
Oh wait, no--
that sounded weird.
I don't mean I
won't try to help
you feel better
if I can...
I just mean I won't
make a big deal because
I'm worried something's
changed between us...
Nothing's
changed.
Yeah, nothin's
Except that now I hate
him more than ever...
Oh, you
think so?!
So do you,
apparently.
Well, for your
information,
I already hated you more
than anything in the world!
That's funny... I
feel the same way.
[Tohru] Well
that's good...
Everything's back
to normal again...
Although, I guess
it really is weird
to be glad that
they're fighting...
[Yuki] Well, it looks
like it's getting late.
We should
head back.
[Kyo] Yeah. We'll go
to the lake tomorrow.
[Tohru]
Okay!
[Yuki] Miss Honda,
are you ready to go?
Uh-huh!
All set!
So you're going
down to the lake?
Better be careful,
Kyo... Don't fall in.
Like I would!
Oh, goodbye Hatori... We'll
see you in a little while...
[Shigure] What is it? Is
he asleep over there?
Uh-huh...
I didn't think
Hatori slept...
Really, Kyo. He's only human.
He has to sleep sometime.
I know that. That's not what
I meant... I'm just saying,
he doesn't seem
like the kinda guy
who'd fall asleep in
front of people...
Ahh... Well... it is
unusual... I'll give you that.
Poor Hari'. He
must be worn out,
what with all
the pressure
he's been under at
the main house...
Oh, here! I
brought a blanket...
I'd really hate for him to
catch a cold or anything...
Tohru, you truly
are amazing...
I envy the man who
marries you someday...
Oh-h! No,
really...!
[Both]
Damn Shigure.
Yes, you deserve
our compliments!
We could all learn something
from this beautiful soul!
What's the matter? You
all look so surprised!
It's because you
appeared out of nowhere!
And you're the last
person we wanna see!
How the hell did
you get in here?!
Come now, Kyo, is it so
difficult to figure out?
If your brain
were working,
you'd know I came in through
the door, naturally!
Dammit! Don't you
even start with me!
Oh, Ayame,
what a--
No, you'll only encourage
him! And he's not staying!
Children... I understand
that my sudden arrival
has you all delirious
with excitement,
but I should
tell you...
I wouldn't be standing
before you now,
if a certain someone hadn't
told me you were here...
"Someone"?
Oh, no... it wasn't me...
Really, it wasn't...
Don't worry, Shigure!
Let them stare!
I'm here now and even if
the rest of the world
should turn
against you,
I will always
stand by your side!
Aya! You are my
strength in adversity!
Je t'aime! Mon
amour! Bon voyage!
Avion!
Ou est la bain?!
Will you quit goofin' around
and tell us why you're here?!
Ah-h, patience,
patience my dear boy...
After all,
as my high school drama
teacher always used to say...
"A man's
true strength
is found in the friends
who support him."
Wise words...
And what's your
point... exactly?
Hmm... I'm
not sure...
Then why'd
you say it?!
Oh, man... I can't
take much more of this,
you're
killin' me...
Do us all a favor,
will ya? Go away.
That's just rude...
And besides,
there's something
I have to do...
Yuki... while I'm here,
it's the perfect chance
for us to deepen our
bond as brothers!
I have a better idea. Why
don't I drown you in the lake.
Anything
you want...
as long as it gives us
some quality time together!
On second thought,
go drown yourself.
Ehhh...
After everything
I've told you,
you're still causing
trouble... Aren't you...
Oh, Hatori! I thought
you were sleeping!
I was, but how can anyone
sleep with all of this noise?
Hey! Good morning, Hari'!
So nice to see you!
Sorry about
waking you up.
I guess I didn't realize
we were being so loud!
Oh, shut
up...
Ayame, what are
you doing here?
Eh?
Well, I was paying a
visit to the main house,
and one of
the servants
(I don't remember his name,
he was an older gentleman),
he told me that you
had gone to the lake...
Naturally, I didn't want
to miss out on the fun,
so...
here I am!
Bastard.
Oh sure. Hatori asks
and he spills his guts!
In any
event...
Yuki, weren't you and Kyo
planning to take Tohru
for a walk around
the lake today?
Oh? A walk
around the lake?
That does sound
like a nice idea...
But I think I
should go along
to help you escort
Miss Tohru...
You know, you can never
be too careful these days,
what with all the weirdoes
out there in the world...
[Both] Yeah...
weirdoes like you!
Oh, uh... thank you, but...
I think we'll be all right!
And we should
really be going!
I've been left
behind, again...
You know, you could
still go with them
if you really
wanted to.
Oh, no, it's quite
alright... In fact,
I'd much rather
stay here...
It's been
far to long
since the three of
us were together...
The night
is long...
and I'm in no mood for
sleep... Shigure...
Aya... you
read my mind...
It seems
tonight,
you and I will be
sharing the same dream...
Yes!
Don't the two of
you ever stop?
A gorgeous view like this, you
almost can't help but smile...
Uh...
or not...
That bastard's going
to be here all night...
He's your brother, isn't he?
So do something about it.
Believe me, if I
could I would...
I hate the way he always
hides behind Shigure...
Yeah, that's
a good one...
You use Shigure to
hide from Akito...
That's not the
same at all!
You should
shut up
until you know what
you're talking about!
I didn't even wanna
know that much!
But I can't get
away from you!
You're every
damn place I go!
So why don't you disappear
for another four months?!
Now you're talkin'! I
would love to disappear!
I'd rather be anywhere
else in the world
right now than
this stupid lake!
You think I
want to be here?
Coming to the lake was the
worst mistake of my life!
We're doing it
again, aren't we?
Miss Honda, it's
not how it sounds!
Don't get the
wrong idea!
I didn't mean that coming to
the lake with you was bad!
I just don't want to
be here with this guy!
Oh, I uh,
I see... eh?
So... you're
okay, right?
Yeah. You're not getting
the wrong idea, are you?
Isn't the
lake beautiful?
Let's try walking
along the shore
for a little
while. Can we?
Sure.
These are
for you.
What's this?
Photographs... They're
Kana's wedding pictures.
It's up to you, whether or
not you want to look at them.
So then... Kana's
gotten married...
I wondered why you
suddenly wanted
to come to the
lake house...
Now I
understand...
I apologize if I was
overly suspicious...
If I'd had
my way,
we would have told you
about this much sooner...
I wanted you to go
to that wedding,
and steal her away from
that idiot of a fiancé!
But Shigure kept me
from saying anything...
There's nothing I
could have done...
No, Kana and I-- it's
over between us...
So...
here.
Well, I for one
can't tolerate this.
You're my friend, so I
realize my opinion is biased.
But even so, what she's done
to you... It's unacceptable.
I can't
stand it...
Kana is able to
find happiness now
because she
chose to forget.
Meanwhile,
she's left you
to carry the burden
of the past, alone...
She left you behind to suffer
with your memories of her.
That's how
it appears...
Tell me... when the snow
melts, what does it become?
Huh? Mmm, Let's see...
It becomes Spring, right?
But... you're
wrong...
You're much more
forgiving than I am...
That's always been
one of the qualities
I admired
about you...
But it's also the
reason you suffer
so much more than
you have to!
I don't think I want
you to get Kana back...
I want you to meet someone
who will make you happy
for the rest
of your life!
I want you to
be, a thousand--
no ten thousand
times happier than
Kana ever will be.
That is what you deserve!
You know... perhaps
you should try
being this determined
with Yuki...
Oh? You think
so? Hm...
You'll find
someone... Someday...
A woman whose love fills your
heart and lifts your spirit,
even when
you're apart...
But whose greatest
gift to you,
will be staying
together...
Spoken like...
a true poet!
Novelist!
A new love...? That
may be more than
I can realistically
hope for...
It may be more
than anyone cursed
by the zodiac
can hope for...
[Shigure] Ah...
they're back.
[Kyo] Shut up!
I wasn't lost!
And when I
think about it...
Isn't it enough to have had a
love like Kana's in my life,
if only for a
short while...?
Is that not already
more than I deserved?
Yes... for now, the
best thing I can do
is keep watch
over the others.
And I will hope that
they never have to know
the same suffering
that I have.
Ah, so they
have returned!
Welcome back, Yuki
and young friends!
Who you callin'
"friend"?
We're back,
safe and sound!
By the way, Yuki... I
was talking with Hari',
and he gave me some
wonderful advice.
And from now on, I'm
going to impress you
with my steadfast
determination...
What "determination"?
Simple... My determination
to forge a bond
with my younger
brother!
This time, I will not
give up until I succeed!
Yuki! As your older brother,
I order you to respect me!
I don't think he
understood what I meant...
No, I don't
think he did...
Ayame!
I turned Ayame into a
snake! What should we do?!
I think we're gonna
lose him for a while.
Well, I can't say
I was too happy
about turning Ayame into
a snake... But overall,
I'd still have to
say it was a very good
first trip
to the lake.
I was so glad to be
able to spend the time
with Yuki
and Kyo.
I almost wish the day
never had to end...
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
Actually Ms. Honda,
she's a tiger.
Huh? A tiger!
Yes, this is
Kisa Sohma.
Kisa isn't
able to answer.
She doesn't speak.
Hatori says the problems
all in her mind.
He said for some reason she's
locked away all of her words.
La, la, la...
Do you have to sing
while you do it?
But even if she
can't speak now,
I just know we'll
get to hear her
sweet little
voice in no time.