I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
Let's see, I'm pretty sure this
is the right section... Ah!
Here it is!
"Fiery Spirit:
The Inner Life
of the Martial Artist"...
Sounds exciting.
My master put
me through hell
up there in the
mountains... but...
those were some of the
best days of my life!
It's like every day was
an adventure, right?
I'd wake up every
morning and ask myself...
"How much stronger
am I gonna get today?"
Just talking about
it gets me pumped up!
Okay, next stop...
Gardening! Hmm...
Oh, hey. This looks
like a good one.
"Twelve Steps To A
Happy Home Garden"
Ah, the base! Those leeks
we picked were delicious.
Are you planting
something new?
Yes, strawberries.
Really? I can't wait!
I love strawberries!
I thought you might....
That's why I'm planting them.
I'm glad I've gotten to know
Yuki and Kyo as well as I have.
But I'd still like to get
to know them even better.
I think I can,
little by little.
And learning more about
the things they like
seems like a good
way to start.
"One Hundred
Family Recipes".
I'll bet there are some
great dinner ideas in here.
I'd like to check
these out, please.
Ah, Miss Honda.
I've been looking for you.
Oh?
You have a phone call
waiting in the staff office.
Come with
me, please?
Yes sir...
This is Tohru...
Grandpa! Hi!
I just found out the
renovations are done.
I uh, I got
a phone call
from my grandfather
up at the school...
He told me.
Ah, I see... And
if memory serves,
you were panning to
move back into the house
once the work was
done, is that right?
What renovations?
Oh, I guess we never
told you, Kyo...
So what?
Tell me now.
Well, you see...
After mom died, I went to
stay with my grandfather,
on my father's side.
But then I found out
my aunt and her husband
were going to move
into the house with us,
and grandpa decided
it would be a good idea
to have some
remodeling done,
you know, to make more
room for everyone.
So he went away
to stay with my aunt
while the work
was going on,
and I stayed here so
I wouldn't miss school.
Well, I didn't
stay here here.
Not at first, I mean. I was
living in a tent for a while...
But anyway, now
that they've finished
with all the
construction,
it looks like I
can go back-
Okay! Enough
already! I get it...
I'm sorry, I just
thought... eh...
Don't mind him.
I think we caught
him a little off-guard
with the
news is all...
We've just witnessed
a classic example
of what I like to call
"misdirected rage".
I believe the technical
term is "being an ass"?
You are so
full of it!
I guess I can understand.
This does seem sudden.
I suppose I should go ahead
and get my things packed
while I still have the
rest of the afternoon.
I'll try to be out of
your way by this evening.
Please, don't hurry
on our account.
Feel free to take as
much time as you need.
Thanks, but I'm sure
they could use my
help straightening
up and everything.
And like the
saying goes:
"never put off 'til tomorrow
what you can do today!"
So then, I'll be right
upstairs if you need me.
Oh, Yuki... Thank you
so much for everything
you've done
for me...
Uh... any time...
A thousand perfectly lovely
things you could have said,
but what poetry spews
from your mouth?
"Any time."
Really, Yuki.
I think that must be the
most unsentimental thing
I've ever heard,
or at the very
least insensitive.
How do you expect to
sustain any sort of,
I don't know, meaningful
relationship...
Aren't you going to try?
To stop her I mean.
Why would I?
We've known from the start
that she was only staying here
until the remodeling
was finished...
Hmm. Well, even so... It does
seem stuffy in here doesn't it?
Let her go...
We should have never
allowed an outsider
in this house
to begin with...
I really had it
wrong this time.
I don't know
why I thought
I'd be able to go on
living here with everyone,
like a family.
Oh, Mom... I can be such a
fool sometimes. Can't I?
You know, this reminds
me of something
that happened when
I was little.
There was that game all
the kids used to play.
"Fruits Basket."
You're an apple.
You're a banana.
You're an orange.
You're a watermelon.
Cherry.
Pear.
Peach.
Tohru, you get to
be the rice ball!
The rice ball! Ooh,
that's sounds yummy!
I guess they were only trying
to tease me a little bit,
the way kids
do sometimes...
But I didn't know that then.
The game went on,
and all the other kids
were called, one by one.
Everyone was running,
and laughing...
And the whole time
I sat there, smiling,
hoping one of them would
shout out "Rice Ball"
so I could play too...
Yeah... Even
since back then,
I've never been very good about
thinking things through...
I should have known.
There was no way I could
have joined the others.
A "rice ball" doesn't
belong in a "fruits basket".
There's some fish left
in the refrigerator.
Eat it soon, so it
doesn't go bad, okay?
And you're almost
out of soy sauce,
so you'll need to pick
some up at the store...
Oh! And don't forget,
they changed the day they
pick up the garbage,
so be sure you put
it out in time...
What else?
Oh... Here!
I wrote down my grandfather's
address and everything.
So if there's anything
you can't figure out,
you know where
to find me!
Thank you, Tohru.
You really are too good to us.
Not at all! I'm the one
who should say that to you!
Uh... And
don't worry.
I won't tell anyone
about your family curse!
Cross my heart
and hope to die!
Speaking of which...
Where's that cat?
I'd think you
know by now.
After all,
sulking on the roof
does seem to be one of
the strange little ways
Kyo shows he cares...
Anyway, good luck
settling into your new home.
Thanks.
Well, as far
as goodbyes go,
that felt pretty
good, I guess...
Although I'd be
lying if I didn't say
it left me feeling a
little bit sad, too...
It's nice to
see you again.
I didn't expect to
see you so soon...
You certainly don't
waste any time.
Ah, Tohru!
Welcome home!
Hi, Grandpa. It's
good to be back.
I hope they
found everything.
I probably should
have stayed
to make sure they had
their dinner, at least.
Hey! Are you done putting
your junk away or what?
I'm sorry! I'm, uh,
I'm almost finished!
I swear. What's the point
of moving into a bigger house
if I'm gonna get stuck
sharing a room with someone?
Just put that stuff
somewhere I can't see it.
Tohru... I'm starving!
What's for breakfast?
I forgot... Our dear, sweet
Tohru has gone, gone away...
That sounded like you
'forgot' on purpose.
No, of course not!
That would be pretty
despicable, don't you think?
But you know,
without Tohru here,
it does feel like all
the fire's gone out
of this kitchen,
doesn't it?
Suddenly it seems
so cold and dreary.
Dammit! You are saying that
on purpose, aren't you?!
In any event, consumed
by grief though we are,
I suppose we can't help but
get hungry at some point...
Which reminds me,
Tohru left us a pot of
her delicious beef stew
in the refrigerator. Yes?
Perfect. Now why don't you
heat that up for us, Yuki?
Your joking, right?
Ah, of course.
You're not too handy in
the kitchen, are you...
Well, Kyo, I guess
that leaves you!
Why do I
gotta do it?!
No, no,
it's all right.
If you don't mind
letting the last
of the wonderful
beef stew
that Tohru put her heart and
soul into preparing for us
get burned to a crisp,
then neither do I.
After all, I suppose
burnt beef stew
will be just as satisfying
as burnt miso soup,
or burnt rice,
or burnt eggs,
or any of the fine burnt
dishes Yuki used to make
for us before Tohru
fell into our lives...
Ah, yes, we all
seemed to do quite well
on our
charcoal-rich diet.
I'm sure there's no
reason we won't grow
accustomed to
it again-huh?
I'd have to rate your
presentation a zero.
Fine! So do it
yourself next time!
We thank you for this stew,
Tohru, wherever you are.
I'm in heaven.
And to think, two bright,
handsome young men like you
couldn't even
find a way
to keep the girl who cooked this
delicious stew from leaving.
Oh, the tragedy...
If she can go back to
her grandfather's house,
there's no reason for her
to stay here, is there?
I'm afraid only our
sorrow will tell us,
as the long lonely hours
without her pass us by.
And our only solace
will be the few scattered
traces of Tohru's presence
left about the house.
Like this cute little
strawberry towel, for instance.
I found it still
hanging in the shower.
I have but to press
it against my face...
and the sweet scent of Tohru
reminds me of happier days!
[Kyo]
You sick bastard!
Say, I found these socks in
my drawer. You put them there?
Oh... is that not right?
Do these really look
like something I'd wear?
I-I'm sorry. I must have
thought they were yours...
Oh, I swear,
what's the use?
Make a note: these are
grandpa socks. Remember that.
Tohru, could you
spare a moment?
Coming!
Could you bring me one of the
big serving plates, please?
Uh... Sure. Okay.
For future reference, we keep
the serving plates over here.
I didn't know it was a full
moon tonight. It's beautiful.
I wonder if Yuki and
Kyo can see this right now.
Maybe we're all looking
at the moon together.
Well, hi there!
Good morning!
Uh... Yeah, hi.
Miss Honda.
Good morning.
And a good
morning to you.
So. How is life at
grandfather's house?
Oh, fine I guess. Everyone's
been really nice to me so far.
They're making me
feel right at home!
That's good. Sounds like
you're fitting right in.
Uh, huh.
[Teacher] In 1687, the Animal
Protection Act was introduced.
This is, of
course, noteworthy,
as it marks
the first time
anything of this
sort was attempted.
Now, the APA,
as I'll call it,
came up once
again in 1770...
So. That's it...
From now on, I guess
I shouldn't expect
things to
be the same
between me and
Yuki and Kyo.
Ah, welcome home!
"Hi Shigure. It's good to be
home." Is that too much to ask?
I've always liked the
cat from the Zodiac!
Right straight!
Really? I can't wait!
I love strawberries!
You can erase
my memory.
But afterwards, promise
you'll still be my friend?
Oh, hello. I'm
back for the day.
Tohru, could
you spare a moment?
Sure...
It's my understanding
that you've been living
in a house with
three men,
is that right?
No way! You were
shacked up!? Nice going!
I had a detective agency
do some checking up on you.
Yeah? No kidding!
So those kinds of things
still exist nowadays?
I don't understand. Why would
you go to all that trouble?
On account of
our oldest son.
It's his dream to
become a policeman.
So you can see how it
might cause a problem
for him, were anyone
in his family
to have a
criminal record...
At first, I did
think hiring
a detective agency
seemed a bit extreme.
Until I remembered how
wild Kyoko was in her youth...
"Like mother, like daughter,"
as they say. Or so I feared.
Now... as long as you
are living in this house,
I have to ask you
not to do anything
so reckless
in the future...
Tell us Tohru...
Living in a house
with three guys?
I'll bet you had all
sorts of fun, didn't you?
Grandpa,
what did you...?
Don't you know how
to do anything
besides
ridicule others?
Tohru, I apologize...
Please don't think
poorly of them...
They're just disagreeable
folks by nature.
Grandpa! What's
gotten into you?
You can't say that!
Tohru?
Please understand, this
family is dear to me.
And this is
where I live.
Even if they do say a
few thoughtless things,
I can
tolerate it.
However, there's no
reason for you
to put up with it to
keep living here.
Y- you want me to-
Ah, it's not
like that.
I'm not trying to
chase you out of here.
It's just that it
wasn't like Kyoko
to put up with anything,
and you are her daughter.
Do you understand?
Kyoko would be more
vivacious living in a place
where she could
spread her arms wide.
Your father would
have said so as well.
My father? Really?
So, if there's somewhere
you'd rather be,
Darling you can go.
But, that
wouldn't be right!
How could I be anything less
than grateful for what I have?
I've been blessed with
a mother who loved me,
two wonderful
friends, Hana and Uo.
What more could
I possibly want
when I have
people in my life
who care about me as
much as they do?
There are so many people
who've been kind to me.
Yuki and the
others... and you!
You've given me a place at your
table, a roof over my head...
I should feel like the
luckiest girl in the world...
I have so much to be
thankful for, right here.
So... where else
would I rather be...?
Except... I didn't think that
leaving Yuki and the others
would make me feel
so... so lonely.
There was still so much I hoped
to learn about all of them...
I wanted us
to go on eating
our meals together,
like a family...
where I could
to talk to them
about so many
things... everything.
The truth of it is, I didn't
want to leave them at all.
I felt like I
belonged there...
I wanted to stay
in that house
with Yuki, and
Kyo, and Shigure...
I wanted to stay.
[Yuki] In that case...
...why not come home?
Yuki--
Who is this?
C'mon. Let's go.
Kyo? You're here
too? But then...
Uh... No wait,
Kyo... I...
I hope you
don't mind.
The door was unlocked so
we let ourselves in...
Can I find Miss Honda's
things upstairs?
Now, just a moment. Who are
you? What is going on here?
Don't worry. We'll be out of
your way before you know it.
Ahh... I get it now.
These must be two of the
guys the little tramp
was shackin' up with.
Don't you ever talk about
Miss Honda that way again.
You low-life.
Uh... um... wait...
Kyo, how did you get here?
What do you mean, 'how'?
You left the directions!
And what kind of a
stupid map was that anyway?
I got stuck having to
walk around half this city
looking for you
with that damn Yuki!
I told you we're going the
wrong way! Now gimme that map!
Uh- uh.
They must have been
fighting the whole way,
and they still
came to find me...
What the hell are
you smiling about?!
Oh, I uh-I'm sorry.
Uh... That's not what
I meant to say. I uh...
What I mean is...
I just...
you know I- I don't even
know why I'm doing this!
It's just, for some reason,
ever since you left,
I've been getting pissed
off about everything!
And I couldn't
figure out why,
so it just pissed
me off even more.
And, really!
If you didn't
want to leave,
you could of said so
from the beginning!
You ever think
about that?!
Wha- but how do you-
We heard you.
Every word.
Ya' know... You can
tell people what you want.
I mean, it's annoying if
you do it all the time...
but I'd say in
your case...
You could stand to speak up
for yourself a little more.
Complain a little, get
upset or something.
Let people know
what's on your mind.
It's what you
gotta do sometimes.
Oh, come on! What did I say?
Why are you crying?!
Can we go? Please,
I... I want to...
I want to go home... Take me
back to the house now, okay?
So walk, already. I'm not gonna
drag you the whole way there.
Rice Ball!
It's true, Mom...
I really must be the
luckiest girl in the world.
I think... I'm
where I belong...
Here. In this house.
With my new family.
It's so good
to be home!
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
[Hana] Perhaps we should
have them invite us over.
I'd like to
see for myself
whether or not, this is
a suitable environment
for you to be living.
[Uo] Hey, great idea.
Let's check it out right now.
[Hana] Wait. If we
show up unexpectedly
they may not
serve snacks.
Ooh! Another good point.
Your two-for-two.
[Tohru] Wait...
[Uo] Okay then, we'll
stay over tomorrow night.
Uh, okay.