I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
Hi there!
It's me, Tohru!
In return for the Valentine's
chocolates I gave him,
Momiji took all of us to a
hot spring for White Day!
It made me so happy that all
of us were able to spend
such a lovely
time together.
And everyone
was so nice to me,
I really felt like I had
become a princess for a day!
But now, Spring
is in full bloom,
and it's the first day
of a new school year!
It's almost
hard to believe,
but we're already in our
second year of high school!
Isn't this
exciting?
And all of the first-years
are just so cute...
I wish you could have seen
them at the entrance ceremony.
You two really
should have come!
[Kyo &amp; Hana]
Whatever.
I shouldn't be
here at all.
I don't know what
I'm allergic to more,
all the damn pollen in
the air, or this place...
So where's the
prince today?
Oh, he's been
busy helping out
with the
Orientation Committee...
Ah, must
be rough.
Seeing as how he
has to deal with
all of the first-year girls'
lovey-dovey attacks...
Um, excuse me...
I think I dropped my
student handbook somewhere.
So why are you
telling me about it?
Is that
bad?
Can you remember
where you saw it last?
Start by looking there... We'll
keep an eye out for it, too.
What's your
name and class?
I'm Arimori Satomi!
Fifteen years old!
I'm a Scorpio,
blood-type B!
I like arts and crafts,
and everyone says
I have really
cute ankles!
Oh! I'm
Sonomiya Rina,
and I was the most popular
girl in my old school!
No she wasn't!
You know Yuki,
one of these days you have
got to tell me your secret.
As popular
as he is,
he's a shoo-in for Student
Council President this year.
Although, I don't think Yuki
would want all that attention.
That reminds me,
at the ceremony,
I thought I sensed
Shigure's electric signals
coming from the
parents' section.
Oh, uh-huh!
He came today...
Actually, there
are two more Sohmas
enrolling with all of
the other first-years.
He wanted
to see them.
Yes, well,
Hatsuharu and Momiji...
they're like younger
brothers to me.
So naturally, I will have to
attend the entrance ceremony.
It's only right that
I should be there
to support them on
such an important day.
Okay, why are you all
staring at me like that?
I hope you're not thinking
I only want to go
to look at all of the
pretty high-school girls?
Tsk, tsk, tsk...
Oh, my word.
You youngsters
of little faith...
What a fool.
Hmm... So there are more Sohmas
starting here this year, huh?
Uh-huh!
Well tell us about 'em.
Are they boys? Girls?
Oh, they're
two more boys...
You don't say... We've
gotta' meet 'em.
I agree. After all,
as upperclassmen,
I'm sure there are many
things we can teach them...
Yeah, I can show them
all the best places
to go skip
outta' class.
Yo, Orange Top.
Go get 'em.
Yes, that's good.
Go get them.
Why do I gotta' do it?!
Make her go and find them!
And what kind of friends
would we be if we did that?
It would be a
terrible crime
to make Tohru go to
all of that trouble.
Well what
about me?!
Oh, you?
That's fine.
Um, you know... I
was already thinking
I'd like to say
hello to everyone,
so I don't
mind going.
Not at all... Really... But
Kyo, if you're going too,
maybe we can look
for them together!
Oh, please...
I already see way too much
of those guys as it is...
But meeting them at school
will be a whole new experience!
It could be
a lot of fun!
Be back soon!
He has a hard time saying
"no" to Tohru, doesn't he?
Very
interesting...
So what class are Momiji
and Hatsuharu in, anyway?
You don't
even know?!
I guess I
wasn't thinking!
Okay... Just wait
here. I'll go ask.
Oh, your kidding!
Really? That's so cool!
Hey... You know a couple
of guys named Sohma?
One of em's got white hair,
the other one's blond?
Ah, yes! They're
in our class!
Go get 'em,
will ya'?
Okay!
Hell, why didn't she ask
where they were before
we started wandering around
the whole damn school?
Hey, man.
Check it out!
That girl's
pretty cute, huh?
Yeah, I guess so. But she
kinda' looks like an airhead.
Yeah! Just
my type.
I'll bet I can talk her
into going out with me.
I don't do so hot
with smart girls.
Well, you have a point there.
So what are you waiting for?
Go over there and
work your magic.
Watch and
learn, man--
On second,
thought, nevermind...
See what happens when you
stand there like a space cadet?
Oh-h...
uh-h, was I?
At least stay alert
when you're by yourself.
Or else, it's gonna
be your own damn fault
when someone
kidnaps you.
You're
right!
I said when
you're alone...?
Right.
You don't have to worry
about it if you're with me.
You can space out
as much as you want.
Right...
And I didn't mean anything
funny by that, either!
I was just sayin'! So
don't get the wrong idea!
Eh? I-- What
do you mean?
Eh... mmm... What
the hell am I saying?
I sound like
an idiot...
Ah, Momiji!
Tohru!
Hi there!
What are
you, stupid?!
Waaaah! Kyo's
hitting me!
Idiot! What the
hell are you doing
wearing a
girl's uniform?!
Um, Kyo,
don't be mad...
Good
morning...
Oh,
Hatsuharu!
Well, at least you're not
wearing a girl's uniform, too.
It's okay, isn't
it? It suits him.
Yeah!
That's right!
Uh huh! It
looks good on you!
What difference
does that make?!
What the... Momiji, what in
the world are you wearing?
Yuki...
Hello
Haru...
So Yuki, are you finished
with all of your work yet?
No, not quite... I was
just making the rounds
and I heard
the commotion.
Hey, listen!
Listen!
I'm really not supposed
to goof around too much
when I'm here...
'Cause if I do, it'll
be too easy for me
to crash
into girls!
So, I'm gonna try to
play it "cool at school"!
How the hell can you call
wearin' a dress "cool"?!
A valid point, Kyo
Sohma, Class 2-D!
And while I find that orange
head of yours disagreeable,
I will ignore it
for the moment...
What I
cannot ignore,
is a boy who would wear a
girl's uniform to school!
This goes
beyond outrageous!
And even if your teachers
allow it, I will not!
For I am this school's
Student Council President-
Makoto Takei!
Also known as... Captain of
the Campus Defense Force!
What a
complete idiot.
I can see already that you're
going to be a problem student!
And the same goes for
you, Hatsuharu Sohma!
I will not tolerate that white
hair! Or those gaudy necklaces!
President Takei...
it's his natural color.
Oh, Yuki, so
nice to see you...
But natural color?! I can see
that his hairline is black!
Yes, that's
natural, too...
That's ridiculous!
I don't believe it!
This is a problem... I guess
we can't really tell him,
"it's because
he's a cow"...
And I suppose wearing
this dress is "natural"
for you,
Momiji Sohma?!
Have you no
pride as a man?!
You had best change your
ways, and your clothes!
Before this incident becomes
the ruin of your life!
But, uh... this uniform...
it looks better on me...
Please, uh... don't
yell at him anymore?
If I am yelling,
Tohru Honda,
it is to be sure he
hears this advice,
which should have been obvious
to anyone with common sense!
[Haru]
Shut up.
Quit shoutin' like you're
king of the freakin' world...
You're makin' my ears
bleed, you bastard!
Now, I've got some
"common sense" for you...
If I wore a tie, it
wouldn't change who I am...
If I had no piercings, it
wouldn't mean I'm "nice"...
And if my hair
was black,
it wouldn't stop me
from kickin' your ass!
Who do you think
you are, anyway?
Do you think
you're God? Huh?
Black
Haru...
What's the matter? Run out of
things to say? No more advice?!
You're not so high and
mighty now, are you?!
Hey, cut it out,
he's just an idiot!
Shut up! No one asked
you, you stupid cat!
Don't call me stupid,
you little brat!
You run away from
our last fight,
and you still think you
can tell me what to do?!
What?! You were the one
who called it off, remember?
Well now I'm
callin' it back on!
That's just
fine with me!
Tohru, do you
want some candy?
Uh... No
thank you...
Hey,
sweetheart...
Leave
them alone!
Tell me
somethin'...
you ladies think Momiji's
outfit is okay, don't you?
In time, after he
grows up some more,
then he'll be able to start
wearing men's clothing.
And if you think he looks
good in that girl's uniform,
just imagine what he'll
look like as an adult.
Lovely...
Don't be
brainwashed!
For now, he should wear the
clothes that look best on him.
No! There's a dress code! It's
not fair to the other students!
You stubborn idiot...
What would you do
if it was Yuki
wearing the girl's
uniform, huh?
Haru, cut it out or
I will cut you off...
Oh, have my words...
made you angry?
It's
beautiful!
Stop imagining me!
Oh, my... I guess I
got carried away...
You are a worthy opponent,
Hatsuharu Sohma... But still...
Your hair is
unacceptable!
And you'll never convince
me that's your natural color!
Impressive
evidence...
there are still many strange
things in this world,
unknown
to me...
He didn't!
I think
he did!
You may have
won today, Sohma!
But you won't be so
lucky next time!
I'll get you!
I'll get you all!
So, who were those
people, anyway?
Beats the
hell outta me.
Umm, Hatsuharu?
I don't understand.
How did you manage
to convince him
that's your natural
hair color?
All right... why don't
you come with me
and see
for yourself?
That Black Haru
is too much...
Um, so how
did he--
Never mind... Don't worry
about it, Miss Honda...
Why do I feel
so exhausted?
Oh, brother... You
think you're exhausted?
Oh! Hey, There's
the bell!
Guess we better get
to our classrooms, huh?
Oh yeah...
If you'd like,
maybe after school I could
introduce you to my friends!
You'd do that?
Really? Great!
I'd love to meet your
friends! I'd love it!
Mm-hm...
Good! They'll
be so happy!
We'll come find you
again later, okay?
Um, actually...
Yuki, Kyo!
I have something I
need to tell you.
Could you stay
for a minute?
Oh... well, that's
all right you guys.
I can go ahead and walk
back to class by myself.
Sorry,
Tohru...
No, don't be silly.
It's all right... Bye!
So... What do you
want to tell us?
This sure as hell
better be important.
Ah... that was quite
a scene back there...
If this is what it's going
to be like every day,
I think it might drive
Yuki and Kyo crazy!
You seem to be in
a good mood...
[Momiji] I heard
he was here...
[Momiji] He's here at
the school... Akito!
Yes, we just found out
about it ourselves...
[Haru] Shigure told
us the news...
right after the
entrance ceremony.
He said Akito decided
at the last minute
he wanted
to come...
He must have come later
than everyone else,
but we think
he's here now...
When we heard, we figured it
was something the two of you
would want to
know right away...
Especially if... you
don't want to see him...
Excuse me,
are you... Akito?
Yes I am...
Miss Tohru Honda.
Pleased to meet you!
I don't believe it! Why would
Akito be here at school?
Oh, I never thought I'd have to
meet him by myself like this...
But, I'm surprised- he looks so
young! And he's handsome, too!
Almost as
handsome as Yuki!
Still, this is the same person
who hurt Hatori's eye...
You're very polite. I'm glad,
you seem to be a good person.
And not only that,
you're extremely cute.
Oh, no!
Not really!
So you're... modest too...
I mean it, you really are cute.
I'm sorry I
didn't say hello
when I saw you at
the main house...
I tend to be rather shy
around strangers...
I hope you're
not angry.
No, no!
Not at all!
Well,
that's good.
I should introduce
myself properly...
I am Akito, head of
the Sohma family...
I'm pleased
to meet you.
Oh no! The pleasure's
all mine, really!
It's strange...
His personality
seems much more gentle
that I imagined...
I do hope you and I can
be friends from now on...
Just as you are with...
Yuki, and Kyo...
Akito!
There you are... I've
missed you, Yuki...
It feels like
such a long time
since we last saw
each other, doesn't it?
What did
you do...?
You look so
grown up now.
I think you've
even gotten taller...
What did
you do?
Tell me, what did you
do to Miss Honda?!
Nothing at all... We were
simply introducing ourselves...
Right,
Miss Honda?
We were just saying
hello, weren't we?
Oh, uh...
uh-huh...
But now that I have
you here, Yuki,
there is something I've
been dying to ask you...
Why did you skip the
New Year's banquet?
Why would you think
to do such a thing?
I've been quite tolerant
lately, have I not?
And the fact that you would
do something like that...
You should know,
it hurts me deeply.
Perhaps... I need to take
some time to re-educate you...
In that little room. The one
I keep especially for you...
[Young Akito] Why don't
you listen to what I say?
I am the head
of this family.
Do you think you
could go against me
and not pay
the price?
[Young Yuki] Ah,
Stop it! Stop it!
Oh, I uh... I'm sorry...
It's just that...
I think we need to be
getting back to class now...
We're
really late...
I understand...
Sorry to keep you.
I suppose I should be
getting back to Shigure
and the others
as well...
they must be
worried by now...
Yuki... I do hope you
enjoy this new school year.
And I would be
very happy
if you paid me a
visit sometime soon...
I can't believe I
just pushed him...
But, Yuki seemed
so frightened...
I felt like I had
to do something.
Miss
Honda...
Yes?
Tell me.
Akito...
He really didn't do... or say
anything strange to you...?
No, nothing... He really
did just introduce himself...
Good...
We should do
something fun!
School gets out early today,
so Uo and Hana thought
it might be nice if we played
a game this afternoon!
Especially since it's
been such a long time...
I think everyone's going to be
there. So you should come too!
[Tohru] I don't know why seeing
Akito scared him so much.
But right now, I just want
to do something nice for him,
to cheer
him up...
I want to take him somewhere
where he can be with friends...
[All] Rock...
Paper... Scissors...
What am I doing here?
I hate badminton!
Oh,
stop it.
I don't even want to hear you
complaining over there...
You're not the one who has to
play with this mask on, wuss!
No one's forcin'
you to play!
So, then... We've picked
teams, but what now?
What are
the rules?
Huh? What are
you talkin' about?
Rules are useless
in badminton.
You hit the birdie
as hard as you can.
Your opponent will
try to do the same.
If you must call
it a rule...
then the first
person to collapse
from
exhaustion loses...
That's good!
It sounds easy!
It sounds
stupid!
Oh, shut up, will ya'?
Just get in position!
Position?
[Tohru]
Okay, all set!
Okay, Prince. Time to
let Orange Top have it!
Keep dreamin'
Yankee!
Are you
ready, Yuki?
[Hana] Here
it comes!
[Shigure] Do you know what
he had to say about Tohru?
He said
she was ugly.
Yes, while we were riding
home in the car today...
She is probably the ugliest
girl I've ever seen...
...and she's not too
bright, either...
I doubt I have anything
to worry about
from a girl
like that.
Yuki won't be interested
in her for long...
And he won't be able to go
against me for much longer,
not if he wants
to be happy...
After all... It's
obvious that Yuki
is still terrified
when he sees me...
I think he remembers where
his true loyalties lie...
It's understandable,
I guess...
With as long as Yuki suffered
Akito's mental abuse...
It's only natural
he'd carry some scars.
But there's something
Akito doesn't understand...
If it's possible for one
person to be hurt by another,
then it's possible for
that person to be healed
by another
as well...
[Shigure] Yes, that is a
comforting thought...
And since we're back
on the subject...
Despite what he said, Tohru is
very cute... In a sweet way...
For some reason...
when you say that,
it reeks of
something illegal.
[Yuki] There are things I have
dreamed about all of my life.
Things I never thought I
would have... Mere fantasies...
Parents that
would embrace me...
A home where I could
truly feel welcome...
A place where everyone could
smile, and laugh together...
A place where I
could be myself,
and I could be close
to the people around me...
A warm place...
surrounded by friends...
But I
know now...
It wasn't
all a fantasy...
That place...
exists.
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
It is an age-old
custom that members
of the royal family should
always wear their hair long,
in honor of the
high king Rurubara,
who, it is said, during the
fourth year of his reign,
was visited by a divine
image -It was Kandra,
shimmering with heavenly
light of red and gold!
Kandra began to chant,
"Ma Rudu Muni!"
And a blue light burst
forth from his forehead.
At this moment, Rurubara's
true spirit was set free!
And just as the vast
springs of strength
and wisdom were
swelling within him,
so too did his hair begin to
sprout forth from his head!
Is that Aya? It is, but
what is he doing here?!