I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
It's really coming
down, isn't it?
And I was going to try
to do the laundry today.
It's not going
to rain all day.
The weather
report said
it should clear up
some this afternoon.
Oh, good. I have to
go to the store, too.
But I don't really
mind the rain.
It just means fall's
right around the corner!
I see. So you
like the fall?
Uh-huh! There's nothing like
a clear fall day, you know,
when the air is
so crisp and nice.
Oh, but then again, I guess
I say that about spring, too.
That's just
like her...
Yuki? You like the
fall too, don't you?
Sure. It's not too
hot, not too cold.
Nope! It's just
right! And Kyo?
What the hell
does it matter?
Oh. Uh,
well I--
It's nothing you've
done, Miss Honda.
Kyo just gets worn out
easily on days like this.
He's a little
out of it.
Eh? Ahh.
Maybe that explains
why he's seemed to be in
such a bad mood lately.
[Tohru] So did you have
a good day today, Kyo?
[Kyo] Nnnn...
It's hard to say, seeing as
how he's always in a bad mood.
Yeah, like you're
one to talk--!
You damn...
you damn rat.
Yuki wasn't
kidding.
He really does get worn
out easily, doesn't he?
Jeez, this
is annoying.
Are you
okay, Kyo?
You know, you
really shouldn't
push your body too
hard. Oh, I know.
Why don't you take a rest
from carrying your umbrella
and share
mine with me!
Seriously?
Uh-huh!
Are you crazy?!
You think I'm so tired
I wanna walk around
lookin' like a sissy under
that girly pink umbrella?
That's a
stupid idea.
Uh... I'm sorry.
Well, maybe... umm...
Maybe if you
transform into a cat,
I can carry you the
rest of the way home!
I mean, you'll still
be sharing my umbrella,
but at least no
one will be able--!
That's even
worse!!
Miss Honda, we
should get going.
Yes, but
what about--
Do you always gotta be
worried about everything?
I mean, c'mon!
Give it a rest already.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry.
You don't gotta
apologize. Let's just go.
Okay. Well, how about
tonight I cook you something
to make you
feel better!
Like...
um... Leeks!
Are you trying
to kill me?!
Oh! I'm sorry!
I wasn't thinking!
Look, just
forget it.
I'll be fine once the
weather clears up.
O-Oh, okay.
[Kyo] Oh sure, now it stops,
after we're already here.
Well, at least the
walk home was quiet.
Huh? You say somethin',
you damn rat?!
Kyoooooo!
Hooray! You're here!
Welcome back, Kyo my love--!!
Uh K-Kyo, I don't think
that's a good idea.
It's not going to hold her
for long, that's for sure.
Kyo? What happened? I...
I can't open the door!
Damn! I can't either! It
must be stuck or somethin'!
Open it.
Allright, so why the hell
are you here, anyway?
Oh, no reason
at all really.
So why bother
comin'?!
What? Is it bad that I did?
I just wanted to see you.
Well, I didn't
wanna see you!
Kyo, why? Why
are you so mean?
You know how
much I love you!?
Yeah! But I got a bad feeling
you're about to show me again!
Shi-gu-re!
Kagura, I wonder
if you'd take Kyo
and run a little errand
for me. Make it a date.
Tohru, you wouldn't
happen to have
this evening's
grocery list?
Huh? Oh, sure!
Right here.
That is, if you
don't mind.
Forget it! We are
not going on a--
All right! It's a
date! It's a date!
I guess my little
plan has succeeded.
[Yuki]
I knew it.
If Kagura gets to spend
some time alone with Kyo,
it ought to calm
her down a bit.
And then she won't
have to smash my house!
Oh, and by the way, try to
be extra careful from now on.
The main house isn't
going to foot the bill
for any
more repairs.
Oh, were they
helping out before?
Right. They were. But I guess
we broke one too many doors.
They've been
sort of reluctant
to give us any
assistance lately.
I had
no idea.
I can't believe I
never knew that before.
I've been living here
for a whole year now,
and this is the first
I've heard of it.
Then again, there are
probably still a lot of things
I don't know
about the Sohmas.
Oh! Well, I guess I can
go ahead and do the laundry.
I think there's some
more rain on the way.
Here's
an idea.
Since Kyo and
Kagura are out,
why don't you and Yuki
go on a date of your own?
A date?! Oh no, really!
I couldn't! I mean, uh--
Yes, let's. We'll
go on a date.
We can take a walk
to the secret base.
Uh... Okay.
There is still a lot I
don't know about the Sohmas.
But I can't give up.
I'm going to keep trying.
I want to know
everything about them.
I want to
understand them.
Even if it takes me another
year, or even longer,
I just have to take
it one step at a time,
and learn
things gradually.
And the
more I learn,
the more I'll be able to see
them for who they really are.
I'd like that.
That's what I want.
Akito, I
have returned.
It seems things have
gone well in my absence.
I must admit,
I was worried.
But he
surprised me,
the expression I saw
on his face today.
Tell me, I've been wondering.
Don't you think it's time?
Time we revealed that
freak cat's true form?
Yes.
I agree. It may
be at that.
I wonder what she'll
do when she sees it?
I can just imagine
the look on her face.
Heh... She won't be
able to stand it.
She'll probably never
be able to set foot
in that
place again.
And when that happens, Yuki
will be very sad, won't he?
Poor thing.
Okay, let's see.
Ah! She's even got codfish
on here, Kyo's favorite.
That's so
like Tohru.
Um, Kyo.
Tohru, she doesn't
know yet. Does she?
You know, you won't be able
to hide it from her forever.
Dammit! Shut up!! That's
got nothing to do with you!
I'm sorry.
But I love you more than
anything in the world!
How do you expect me to
pretend like I'm not worried!
Uh-oh! C'mon! We
better get moving
before you cause a scene.
Uh, let's go this way.
Why?
Why do you care so
much about me, anyway?
It's crazy!
Most people...
Most people don't wanna
have anything to do with me.
I mean, so what
is it with you?
I--
Kyo, you don't
remember, do you?
Remember what?
It's a secret. Besides, you
wouldn't believe me anyway.
♪ Well, we'd better
go get in line! ♪
Hey! What
is it?!
♪ Come on, Kyo! ♪
Hey!
[Kagura] Aww. It looks like
it's about to rain again.
[Kyo] You're not gonna
tell me, are you?
Let's walk home
holding hands!
There is no
way in hell.
Why not?! You
never minded before!
We used to
always hold hands!
'Cause you made me! And it
was only like 3 or 4 times!
Oh,
Kyo...
...you're
so mean.
All right, I'll do it!
I'll hold your damn hand!
But just for a
little while, okay?
Kagura!
'Kay!
Most people don't wanna
have anything to do with me.
I mean, so what
is it with you?
You really don't
remember, do you?
Kyo... The truth is.
It's because of you.
That very
first time...
You held out your hand and
you asked me for mine.
Come on,
Kagura!
It was your
hands, Kyo.
I believed in
them. I believed.
Come on,
Kagura!
Oh... look. It's
starting to rain again.
I wonder where Kyo
and Kagura are.
I hope they make
it back okay.
Even if Kyo collapses,
Kagura can carry him home.
Right.
Oops,
sorry.
So you've
finally come back.
Um, is this
someone you know--?
[Kyo] Cut it
out, dammit!
[Kagura]
Wah-hah-hah.
[Kyo] I said a little
while, and I meant it!
You're lucky I even
went as long as I did!
Now enough is enough,
woman! That's it!
[Kagura] Aw, Kyo!
You're no fun at all!
Kyo.
Master?
You're looking
well, Kyo.
Kazuma. I'm glad to see
you've made it back safely.
Yes, thank you. And you,
Shigure, I've heard that
your writing career is
coming along quite nicely.
Haha- Well, it's
been all right.
So this man is Kyo's
martial arts teacher.
It's good to see you again,
Master! It's been so long!
It has been a
long time, Master.
Yes it has, indeed.
Hello, Kagura.
And Yuki. It
seems you've grown
quite a bit since
I last saw you.
[Tohru] Um,
excuse me.
I'm sorry. Tohru,
this is Kazuma Sohma.
Kyo's told you about
him before, I believe.
He's his teacher. And
he's also the man
who taught martial arts to
Yuki, Kagura, and Hatsuharu.
I see.
That's amazing!
So, then. You must be the girl
I've heard so much about.
Oh uh, it's nice to
meet you. I'm Tohru Honda.
So you are...
so you are.
I understand that
you've come to learn
of the Zodiac
Curse. Is that right?
[Tohru] Uh...
uh-huh.
[Shigure] Kyo.
You're being awfully
quiet over there.
Don't you at least
want to say hello.
I mean, you haven't seen
him since your training
in the
mountains, right?
How long has that
been? A year?
Ah-
Uh Kyo,
wait!
Perhaps you could tell me
where I might find Kyo's room.
Oh, uh-huh.
It's upstairs.
Kyo, I'm
coming in.
Ah, I'm glad to see you've been
keeping up with your reading.
Master, I'm sorry
if I was rude.
You're still reluctant as ever
to speak out in front of Yuki.
That's all right.
I understand.
Master, it's
good to see you.
You too.
[Tohru] Sooo
your master,
he's not a member of
the Zodiac, is he?
No, but still,
he's always had
really close ties
to the main house.
You see, before Kyo,
Master's grandfather
was the one who carried
the curse of the cat.
I guess that's why he
always seems to understand
what Kyo's going through
better than anyone.
But, more than that,
Master's always been
a very important
person in Kyo's life.
They're very close.
Master looks after him,
and protects him, just
like a real father.
Just like a
real father.
[Kyo] So does this mean
you're back for good?
Are you done with
your training?
That's right.
I don't think
I can get away with keeping
the dojo closed much longer.
Well, then, I'm comin' back
to the dojo with you, right?
Just like we talked
about before!
When I return, we will
live together again.
But until that day
comes, farewell.
No, Kyo. You will
continue living here.
What do you mean?
You promised!
This is the best place for
you right now, I think.
The environment here
has done you good,
and will continue
to do so.
I think you know it too.
Whether by coincidence or fate,
I believe that
you have come
to live in this
house for a reason.
But I hate it here! Even
the damn air in this place!
It's smothering
me! I hate it.
I just wanna
get outta here.
No, I don't think it's that
at all, Kyo. It's not hate.
[Kagura] Say,
do you know if
Master's planning
to spend the night?
[Tohru] Uhh,
I don't know.
I guess I'll have to get a
place ready for him if he is.
[Kagura] Okay.
I'll go ask him!
Tonight, I plan
to do it tonight.
And whatever happens, I thought
I should warn you in advance.
I see. So what led you to
this decision all of a sudden?
Today, looking
at his face,
I saw something there
I didn't expect to see.
I think this girl could open
his heart, and accept him.
The time to
act is now.
While the opportunity exists,
or so I have determined.
So many of our hopes have
been placed in her already.
Now she carries
yours as well.
Kazuma, are you truly prepared
to trust her with everything?
You do know,
there's a possibility
that this will fail,
despite your intentions.
And if that happens, this
time, it could break him.
To the point where he
will hate even you,
and never
smile again.
And knowing this... you'd
still risk everything
for this
one chance?
Uaaa! What the
heck happened?
How'd you manage to
burn it so bad, Master?
You're not very good at this
sort of thing, are you?
Hmm. Well, when it comes
to the culinary arts
perhaps I could
use more training.
I know the risks. Even so, I
want to take a chance on her.
And Tohru, what
will this do to her?
This is bound to cause
her a great deal of pain.
But still...
Yes?
I wonder if you might be so
good as to loan me a moment
of your time
this evening.
Sure.
Master...
If there's somethin'
you gotta tell me,
maybe you better
do it inside.
You know what it does to me
when the weather's like this.
Yes, I do. It was the
same with my grandfather.
This sort of weather sapped
him of his strength as well.
I suspect the Zodiac
Cat in its original form
must have also
hated the rain.
If you don't soon learn
to accept the fact that
"original form"
is a part of you,
you will never
move forward.
I have
accepted it!
But what does
it matter...
My life was over
before it even started,
the moment I was born
with this curse...
And you
know why?
It's because of
that damn rat!
It's that damn rat's
fault! For everything!
You haven't
changed.
Is this the way you
intend to go on living,
for the rest
of your days?
...ears
plugged...
...eyes
closed...
Hiding... behind your
hatred for Yuki...
Is that the only
way you can justify
shutting yourself off
from the world... Is it?
What, then... Will you
simply wait for death?
Completely alone?
Just like my
grandfather...
You said before that
you hate it here.
Well, I don't
believe that's true.
You don't
hate it...
But you're afraid to face
what you know you must...
So instead,
you run away...
The air that you said
was smothering you...
You know that it could
also heal you...
But you refuse
to let it...
You refuse to let anyone see
you for your true self...
You're too afraid of
what you might lose...
You're running away
because you're afraid
to admit your feelings,
even to yourself.
You're
wron--
And so... I will grasp your
hand as you turn to run...
And though this path
may lead to ruin..
I will lead you to
it's end... Kyo...
We will
discover now,
whether your life was truly
over before it began...
It's all
right...
It's all right, because
I love you... So...
That's why I don't want
anyone to see you...
No one...
My child...
Don't look
at him!
It's disgusting.
Don't look
at me!
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
And so... you've seen
Kyo's other form,
the one he has kept
hidden from you.
It is part of the burden
he bears as the Cat,
that he is also cursed to
take this grotesque shape.
Do you find
it revolting?
Is it
frightening to you?