I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
[Child] Tohru, you get
to be the rice ball!
[Kyo's Mother] Kyo...
Has something happened?
What's the matter?
Did Akito say something to
you again? It's all right...
It's all right...
Because... I...
I still love
you, at least...
I still love you
more than anything...
You're still human...
just like everybody else.
It's okay. I'm not the
slightest bit afraid of you.
No... You really were
afraid of me, weren't you...
That's why you checked me
dozens of times a day,
to make sure my beads hadn't
come off or anything...
You're my son. I'm
so proud of you.
In that case, why didn't
you ever let me go out?
You're so adorable, I wanted
to keep you all to myself!
You were
ashamed of me...
No, I
love you!
I would die for you,
I love you so much!
Why is that all
you ever said?
You never really accepted
me-- not the real me...
You were just saying
all the things
you thought a mom
was supposed to say.
Your mother loved
you more than anyone.
Stop!
You too...
Is that all we
do... is run away?
Is that
all we do?!
Well I for one am
tired of running!
I don't want to
do it any more!
Miss Honda... Tell him...
Tell him the truth...
Tell him what you
think, right now!
Just tell
him the truth!
Hm! Thanks for
the warning!
You suck.
[Kyo] Let people know
what's on your mind.
[Mrs. Honda] Just
be yourself.
[Kyo]
It's okay...
Complain a
little...
...get upset or
something... It's okay...
You can tell people
what you want, you know.
Let's go home...
Back to our house...
I'm sorry... I'm... I'm such a
fool. I don't know what to do.
I'm afraid... Right now,
Kyo... I'm afraid of you.
But...
still...
I want us to stay
together... Together!
I do...
Always...
I want to eat our meals
together and study together
and worry
together...
I want to tell you all the
things that are on my mind.
And Kyo, I want to
listen to you...
And so... I want us
to stay together!
It's okay... You
don't have to...
You don't have to
love everything.
If you're
afraid...
it just proves that you've
truly seen the real me.
Not like
my mom...
She went through all the
motions of loving me...
but she never even
tried to see me.
I wanted us to talk together
and worry together, too...
I was fine with
her being afraid.
Even if she didn't love
me in that ugly form...
I wanted... I wanted
us to stay together...
I've been
a fool...
I didn't think
that... anyone...
anyone... would
ever say that to me.
Not to
me...
Tohru...
How is it
that you...
could
give me...
...the words that I needed
to hear the most right now?
How is it that...
somebody like you...
could be here by my
side... crying for me?
How...?
Yuki...?
Thank you.
No, Kagura...
Oh, Mom...
You're not even
saying goodbye...?
I know... I'm still
not good enough...
But someday... I swear,
someday I'm gonna be!
I'm gonna be the
kind of person
my master can be proud
to tell the world...
"I'm his Dad!"
You haven't
changed...
You are still quite the
troublesome son... Kyo...
Mom...
Is there
anything I can do?
Just be yourself.
You'll be fine.
[Akito] It serves you
right, you know...
♪ Breakfast time, breakfast
time, all for me, breakfast-- ♪
Kyo, it's time to eat.
You're sure are
lively this morning.
Let's
see now...
Ah! Where
to start...
Shigure...
Well,
um...
Tomorrow... I'd like to go
see Akito, if that's okay.
Can I talk to you
outside for a moment?
About Akito...
The reason he only has a
short time left to live...
is because he bears
what you might call
the "core" of
the Zodiac Curse.
This was decided at
the time he was born.
And despite what
you may hope,
there's nothing he or any
of us can do to change it.
All we can do...
The Sohmas, I mean...
is live the way
he tells us.
But that's us...
As for you...
I think it might be best if you
stayed away from him... okay?
Okay...
[Shigure] Ah, hello. Ha'ri!
Uh, we're on our way over now,
if that's
okay...
Oh, no, uh... It's not
so much for me, as uh...
as it is
for Tohru...
I admire
your nerve...
What have you
come here for?
Go on... tell me...
I won't be angry...
What have you
come here for?
I don't
know...
It's not that you
don't know, is it?!
You just can't
say it, can you?!
Well, let me
say it for you!
You're going to tell me that
you want to go on living
with everyone
in that house!
But I won't
allow it.
I will make
you regret...
you ever had anything
to do with the Sohmas!
You will suffer! You will
suffer as we suffer!
Did you think, by coming
here and kneeling before me
you could
change anything?!
Well let me tell
you, you can't!
None of you can! You can
never leave the Sohmas!
Just like you can
never go against me!
Now... I want to hear you
beg me for forgiveness...
Say you'll never interfere
with the Sohmas again.
It must have been very
painful... Akito...
being told that the
day you were born...
you were going
to die...
It must have been
so painful...
What was?! What do
you know about it?!
You're right... I
can't even imagine...
how awful it would be to
know something like that...
or how
terrifying...
Shigure... and
Yuki... and Kyo...
I'm sure they feel
the same way...
And Hatori,
too...
And when you pass
away, we'll be sad...
we'll be very sad
to lose you...
And so...
Who's going to be sad? Everyone
is able to live, thanks to me.
They all hope that I
will be gone quickly.
I was born in order to die...
That's what was decided.
But, why... Who decided
it had to be like that?
Akito, right now, you're
alive, aren't you?
Alive? You call this
being alive? Do you?
It's been decided...
It's been decided!
And they never
even asked me...
I... I didn't know my
Mom was going to die...
Silence! Stop
talking! Hatori!
I want you to erase this
girl's memory! Do it! Now!
Hatori!
I wanted her to
live a long time...
I wanted her... to be
here, to watch me...
Stop crying... Stop
it! Stop crying!
And I don't know what your
family's curse is... but...
I'm happy... I'm happy
that I know you... Akito...
And I don't regret
meeting you...
or anyone...
not at all...
I want to know you... Please
tell me how you feel...
Even if you're
angry, or bitter,
or frustrated...
that's okay!
Because the important
thing is...
right now, Akito...
...you're alive.
I don't
know...
[Kyo]
Hey!
Well, c'mon you damn rat! Tell
me what happened in there!
Oh, uh...
Nothing really...
I guess it was
presumptuous of me to think
anything would change
if I came here today.
Oh, no... That's
not true at all...
Indeed,
it's not...
What're you
talkin' about?
[Shigure] Oh, uh... nothing.
Just thinking out loud.
[Kyo] No you
weren't!
[Tohru] Um... I promise
to tell you everything
once we get
home, okay?
And Kyo...
What do
you want?!
We should have a fight
once we get there, too.
Heh! So you're finally
ready to face the music, huh?
Well it's
about time...
Hey! Hold on! I'm not
lettin' you out of my sight!
I see he's feeling
lively again today...
Yes, well, you seemed pretty
lively yourself, back there.
I suppose...
Not that it really made that
much of a difference...
It's still not too
late, you know...
We may be able to find
something, even now.
Yes. So long as we can decide
what it is we're looking for...
And even if we can't, there's
always the next time around.
Yes, there is... Shall
we take it slowly, then?
[Kyo] Hey!
Can we hurry
up already?!
I don't care if it's
leftovers or what,
I gotta eat! I'm
starvin' over here!
Oh...
coming!
Mom...
...are you
watching?
You know, sometimes
things are hard,
and I feel sad, or
I want to cry...
...but I'm
still trying...
we're all trying to
keep moving forward...
and we will...
I know we've still got
a long way to go...
together.
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.