I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
[Tohru] This year
has gone by so fast.
It seems like December
just came and went
in the blink
of an eye...
It's already the
last day of the year,
the day we do our
New Year's cleaning.
Dammit, can't you
do anything right?
You're the last person I
need to hear from right now.
What's that supposed to mean?!
You tryin' to start something?!
Quit horsing
around, you two.
Who asked you,
you dirty bitch!
You gonna talk to me like
that after I came here
to help you out of the
goodness of my heart?
I... uh... I'm
sorry about that.
Oh, it's okay... It was just a
little tear. It's easy to fix.
I think I'm going
to wet my pants.
Didn't you see what the sign
said? "Closed for cleaning".
Uhh...
Right, well...
It's closed
for cleaning.
I just need
a minute...
Did you know?
In many ways,
the flow of electrical
waves through our bodies
can be compared to
the flow of water...
Over 60% of the human
body is made up of water.
In other words, if you were
to round up, people are water.
Many people fail
to realize this,
considering the body's
solid appearance.
But nonetheless, on the inside,
we are essentially a liquid.
Water is continually
flowing through us.
It streams
through our veins.
It sustains all
parts of our bodies:
the head, the
heart, the stomach,
the kidneys,
the bladder...
Shigure!
I need the last 500
pages of your book!
I already had to make
excuses to the print shop
to get them to
wait until today.
I mean, we can't
release the book
with the last half of the
pages blank! It would be the--
Ah,
Shigure!
Just in time!
Give us a hand!
Put your
backs into it!
Hey!
Shigure!
Mii, come grab
that end!
You should be working
on your manuscript!
Come on,
hurry!
Right!
What do you think
we should have
with the New Year's
soba noodles?
Any ideas?
Let's see... maybe
some onions, some fish...
...and bean
sprouts...
...ah, and
some tempura...
Heave! Ho! Heave! Ho! Heave!
Huh?! He's gone! Where is he?!
Hold on!
You're gonna
drop it!
Tim-ber!
Ah... Lovely. They
smashed the house again.
It's your fault! Your end
fell first, you damn rat!
Really? Your eyes must be as
weak as your arms, stupid cat.
Um, excuse me, but
is everyone okay?
[Kyo] That's it!
Let's go!
Why does it
always gotta be me?
Now get off your ass
and start cleaning it up!
Shigure!
There!
Good as new!
Shigure!
Shigure!...
You clumsy idiot!
It's not
my fault!!
What do you think
you're doing?!
Oh, I was just feeling
a bit hungry...
Five hundred pages! Not five!
Five hundred! I need them now!
You don't have
time to be hungry!
Of course, of course!
I'll get right on that.
But one thing
before I start...
I just need one
little favor-
could you hold your
hands out for me?
Once I see that, I'll be
able to write, no problem.
Is that
a fact?
Now, just put your
head down a bit.
Donations for the
poor beggar girl?
If you're
not helping...
you could at least
get out of the way.
You're the last person
I need to hear from.
Tohru, maybe you'd better
go on and do your shopping.
Oh, good idea.
Shopping? Great! But
you'll need someone
to help carry
your things.
I'll go too!
Oh, Tohru. I'm sorry.
Something's come up.
You'll have to find someone
else to go with you...
Your hands! Your fingers!
Start moving them! Write!
It's strange.
For some reason,
with you standing over my
shoulder like this... well...
It's stifling my
creative spirit.
The ideas
aren't flowing
through the pen
like they should...
I don't want
ideas! I want ink!
It's way to late
for you to be
worrying about your
creative spirit!
Perhaps I should go in
search of quiet inspiration.
All right!
I'm leaving!
But you'd better be
writing when I come back.
At last.
It's perfect.
No, wait... I'm sensing a
second bathroom... Upstairs...
HEY!!
There... That
looks much better.
[Grocery Clerk] Come inside!
Don't miss your last chance
to take advantage of
our New Year's specials!
So, Miss Honda, what
are you going to make?
New Year's
cakes!
Uh? New
Year's cakes?
Uh-huh! I just
hope I picked
out ingredients
everyone likes...
Shigure, Kyo, and I
will be going back
to the main
house tonight...
I'm sorry...
I really should have
explained earlier,
it's sort of a Sohma
family tradition...
I, uh... I guess it was
just such an obvious thing
to us that
we'd be going,
that we completely
forgot to mention it...
That's all
right...
But in that case, I guess I'm
getting a little too much, huh?
Oh! Yuki!
Behind you! Look out!
I'm sorry
about this...
I was supposed to carry
your things for you.
Oh, no, I don't mind. Really,
it's no trouble at all...
[Mii] Shigure!?
Shigure!?
Shigure!
Ah, Mii. Be a dear and hand
me that newspaper, would you?
Ah! Research
materials, right?
You're working
so hard!
Of course
I am.
I have to get ready for
New Year's too, you know.
Mii! Give me
back my kite!
I'm not giving this to you
until you're done! I mean it!
Not until you are
100% finished!!
If you want it
before then,
you'll have to kill
me to get it back!
[All] Thank you
for this food!
S- Shi- gu- re...
Well, hello Mii... You look
tired... Come in, have a seat.
Ah... I'm so full!
Now I can spend
the rest of the year
without a care
in the world...
You can't say
that until after
you've finished
your manuscript!
Still, you can't deny
the soba was delicious.
Now you listen to me! The
situation is critical here!
Don't you understand? We
have a deadline to meet!
You can't afford to waste
time on silly things
like soba noodles
or New Year's...
In fact, I think
I'd eat it everyday
if it weren't for what
it did to my nails...
Nails?
Well, if you eat
too much soba,
your fingernails start to
smell funny, don't they.
Ahh, Mii... you're
such a good sport.
It's hell... I'm in
hell... I just know it...
eternally damned...
fire and brimstone...
burning flesh...
"abandon all hope"...
Hey...
That writer guy asked
me to give this to you.
Hm?
You mean it was finished? Why
didn't he just tell me? Why-y?
Oh, New Year's cakes...
They look delicious.
You think so?
I do. But, I have to wonder
if that will be enough
for the four
of you...
Oh... No, I just made
enough for myself.
Yuki and the others are going
to be spending New Year's
at their
family's estate...
Okay, it's almost
time to go...
Don't you think you
two ought to get ready?
Hm?... Yuki, Kyo...
We're going to be late.
[Both] Shut up...
I'm not going.
Oh, Tohru,
it's terrible...
Neither one of these
two wants to go with me
back to
Sohma House...
Dammit, quit whining! You're
supposed to be an adult!
Um... You're
not going back?
I haven't been to that
place in four months.
I'm not
gonna go now
just 'cause of some
stupid New Year's thing.
I had my reasons
for leaving home.
They'd seem almost meaningless
if I went back tonight...
Why do you have
to be like this?
You've both gone every year
before now, haven't you?
You see... New Year's is a
big night for the Sohmas...
It's the one holiday that
the entire extended family
gets together
to celebrate.
That does
sound big.
Just getting through
all the introductions
can be an event
in and of itself...
But I'd have to say
the real highlight
of the evening is
the Zodiac Banquet.
A banquet?
Yes, and it's probably
the most important part
of the Sohma New
Year's celebration.
As the name
might imply,
it's a banquet that only
members of the zodiac
are allowed
to attend...
The zodiac member of the new
year performs a dance...
This year it's
Momiji's turn.
Ahh... but
nothing can compare
to the beautiful dance
Yuki did three years ago...
I wish I could
have seen it!
I told you never
to talk about that.
Right.
It all sounds
so wonderful...
A Zodiac Banquet, just
like in the old folktale!
[Kyo] It doesn't
matter to me.
I mean, it's not
like I can even go
to that stupid
banquet anyway...
What? But,
why not?
It's been a
long-standing rule
that the Cat isn't
allowed to attend...
And, I suppose
that's in keeping
with the old folktale
as well, isn't it.
I'm sorry...
Ah, it's nothing you gotta be
getting all upset about...
I don't care.
It's not the reason
I'm not going back,
if that's what
you think.
I think he's afraid
he'll get hurt,
what with Kagura being
so excited to see him...
Shut up!
In any event... If we go
back to Sohma House tonight,
we'll have to stay until
the third, won't we?
So for
three days
we'd be leaving Miss
Honda here all alone...
Stupid cat. Did you
just realize that?
Don't call
me stupid!
Then don't act
stupid, Stupid.
Um, please wait, you two...
Thank you for worrying...
But you don't have to.
I'll be all right.
It's funny, but
just knowing
that you're both
thinking about me, well...
I'm so happy! And I want
you to be happy too,
so you should go,
enjoy yourselves.
I mean, this is your
family's special night.
And you'll get to
see your parents
for the first time
in a while, right?
I'm sure they're all looking
forward to seeing you...
Promise, I'll
be fine...
And I'll take great care of
the house while you're gone...
You are talking
to the girl who--
Aah! The bathwater!
I left it running again!
If that doesn't inspire
confidence, nothing will.
Okay...
I'll go back.
Guess I've
got no choice.
If it's what
she wants...
...and when she says
it like that, and all...
[Tohru] Try to be careful.
Watch out for all the crowds.
We'll be fine... There won't
be many people out right now...
You be careful, too. Make
sure you lock all the doors.
Okay...
Be safe!
You know, she always
used to leave that window
in her room
wide open...
What were you
doing in her room?
I wasn't! I saw
it from outside!
She can be rather
careless at times...
This morning, she tripped
on the stairs again...
And she's always bumping
into the walls and stuff...
Clumsy as
she is,
if there was a way to choke
on rice, she'd find it.
Don't even joke
about that.
You two...
You sound like a couple of
old ladies, the way you worry.
Don't get
me wrong,
I understand your
concern for Tohru...
but you've already
made the decision
to go back to
Sohma House...
Now hold on! Who
said I was concerned?
Stop talking
nonsense! Let's go!
Oh! Now that I
think about it...
there was an article
in the evening paper
about a rash of burglaries
in the neighborhood...
The culprit is still at
large, or so they say.
Oh, great. If a
burglar came to the house,
she'd probably open up the
front door and invite him in...
She'd give him a seat at
the table and serve tea!
Then, knowing her,
she'd want to hear
the burglar's
whole life story.
Well. Let's be on
our way, shall we?
If you two just
stand there
in the middle of the
street like that...
...you'll
get run over.
O- oh, Saki. What a
pleasant surprise.
[Kyo] Why can't she just say
"hello" like a normal person?
[Yuki] Where in the world
did she get that cloak?
Can we help you
with... something?
Yes...
Perhaps.
Are you looking
for Tohru, maybe?
...She's still
at the house.
We were just on our
way to visit our family.
I see... Then
for her,
this will truly be a
lonely New Year's...
Until now, Tohru
and her mother
have always spent New
Year's Eve together...
But this is the first year
since her mother's death...
This is the first new
year she will ever see
without her loving
mother at her side...
Instead, she will have
to spend this night alone.
I offered to stay with her,
but she wouldn't hear of it...
She just smiled, and told me I
should be with my own family...
But what about her? What
family does she have tonight?
And how will she feel,
sitting there by herself,
remembering all
of the New Year's
she shared
with her mother,
and will never
share again?
How will she feel when the New
Year's bells begin to chime,
the same bells she
used to stay up late
to hear with
her mother...
How did she feel? Standing
there as we were leaving...
...when she was smiling
and waving goodbye...
Do you really think she'll
be unaffected by that?
Do you really think
she'll be all right?
How does she
feel, right now...
...all alone in
that house...?
Do I even want to
know what happened?
I can
explain.
What are you doing? You know
Akito's just gonna get pissed!
Kyo bumped his head
as he was standing up...
And what about you? I wouldn't
keep Kagura waiting...
The thing he bumped into
was Yuki's right cheek.
This happened due to the
fact that both of them
started moving at
the same time.
End of
commentary.
[Kyo] Shut up! Why
don't you go see her
if you're so
worried about it.
[Yuki]
I'm busy.
Um, wait a minute. Where
are you going, exactly?
I'm going home!
So, Saki. I'm suddenly under
the distinct impression
that you had all of
this planned out.
I didn't really know what
would happen if I came...
I only knew that I wanted
to do something for Tohru.
And that
is all.
I wish you pleasant electric
waves, this coming year.
I'm not sure what to
make of that one...
Why?
Why didn't I
realize sooner?
I just didn't
see it...
But how could I? She looks
so happy all the time...
Whenever I see her,
she always has a smile.
Sometimes, it seems like
even the simplest thing
can make her
smile for hours...
But still...
Saying she doesn't mind being
alone-- that she's all right...
[Both] There isn't
a person alive
who'd really
feel that way!
Oh, it's you. You startled
me... But why are you--?
Oh, no, no! I wasn't crying,
really! It's just, well...
You know, it's the
holiday season and all,
and you know how they
say people can get
a little emotional
this time of year...
Thank goodness.
If we'd kept
on going...
If we hadn't stopped
and turned around...
We would have left her
here, crying by herself.
What's wrong?
Are you all right?
We have to watch
the first sunrise...
Yeah, and I wanna
have some more
of those New Year's
soba noodles...
[Yuki]
I'm home.
[Kyo]
Welcome home!
Ah, Shigure!
Good to see you!
Shigure!
Momiji.
Hello.
Uh... Where's
Yuki and Kyo?
They both decided... they'd
rather stay home tonight...
But, I for one am looking
forward to watching your dance.
Wouldn't miss
it for the world.
Akito...
Yuki and Kyo...
They aren't coming.
What do
you mean?
Well, how should I
say this... I guess...
there's no point in
making excuses...
They skipped out.
So... you
talked to Hana?
We... sort of ran
into her on the way.
Is that right?
Oh, Hana...
I promise,
you'll be the first
person I call this year!
I'll be
waiting...
But, uh... Are you
sure this is okay?
I mean, what's the rest of
your family gonna think?
They won't mind that you
stayed here, will they?
I don't want you to get
in any trouble over me...
It's no
trouble...
We'll just go
back sometime
before the third and
visit with everyone...
Probably...
Oh...
okay.
I imagine the banquet is in
full swing, right about now...
Even so...
I'm actually kind
of glad I missed it...
I don't feel guilty
for not going...
It's kind
of funny...
I thought I had so
many important reasons
for not wanting
to go back...
...but,
truth is...
Hey, look you two!
The sun is coming up!
Have you decided
what to wish for, yet?
I've got mine
all ready to go!
The truth
of it is...
...maybe, all I
really wanted...
...was to spend New Year's
together, with her...
This year I'm gonna
beat that damn rat!
Ah, you are wishing,
aren't you?
And so, here we are, at the
start of a whole new year...
It's such a
beautiful sunrise.
And seeing it with Yuki and
Kyo-- it means so much to me...
I just know it's going
to be a wonderful year!
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
[Haru] Have you ever heard of
a place called Sohma house?
Sohma house?
[Torhu] So then, by any
chance are you a Sohma?
Wow, so if he's part
of the Sohma family
then maybe he's a part
of the zodiac too!
[Yuki] So now
it's Haru?
They just keep
showing up don't they?
[Tohru] He's
so polite.
He seems like he's
a lot more grown up
than you'd expect
someone in middle school.
[Haru]
Heh! You're not a man!
You're a little kitty cat
who's too scared to fight!
[Kyo] You little punk!