I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
Hi, I'm
Tohru Honda.
Eighteen months ago, I lost
my mom in a car accident.
I should feel depressed.
But I'm not, really.
I can still enjoy watching
the clouds float by
on a beautiful
day like today.
And the reason I'm
able to smile, I think,
is because I've gotten
to share so much time
with the wonderful
Sohma family.
No!
Oh no! My bag...
my bag has torn.
Here! Let me help
you with that!
No, please. You
don't have to.
I don't want to put
you to any trouble.
It's okay! I don't mind
at all! I'm happy to help!
I am so,
so sorry.
I can't seem to go anywhere
without causing problems
for everyone
around me.
I'm just a born
troublemaker, I suppose.
It's true. I'm so worthless I
can't even carry a paper bag.
I don't deserve to
share the same air
with the rest of
the human race.
I'm a blemish on the face of
the world. What was I thinking?
A low-life like me should never
have come to visit Shigure.
Aaaaah! I'm sorry! I
apologize to the world!
To the whole
universe!
I'm sorry I
came here today!
Um... Are you...
are you Ritsu?
Aaaaah! My
reputation precedes me!
I'm so infamous that
even a complete stranger
knows my name!
I'm such a terrible
person! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry world!
I apologize to all the
people who are forced
to share the
same name as me!
I'm begging of you!
Please! Forgive me!
[Tohru] So this
is Ritsu...
My, this is unexpected.
The ever-timid Ritsu
has decided to venture
out and pay me a visit.
Oh...
yes... I...
I'm... s-sorry for all
the trouble I caused Tohru
in front of
the house...
Oh no, please...
It was no trouble!
I'm just happy
to have finally
gotten a chance
to meet you!
You are?
Yes, and you seem like
a really sweet girl.
I first heard about Ritsu
on my trip to the hot spring.
She's the daughter of that nice
hostess who runs the resort.
Aaaah! I'm
sorry! I'm sorry!
You remind me so
much of your mother,
from the first
instant I saw you,
I knew right away
who you were!
Oh, and another thing--
Ritsu is also a member of
the zodiac! She's the monkey!
Did you know
that my own child
is a member
of the zodiac,
just like Master
Yuki and the others?
Yes, my child was born
under the sign of the monkey.
By the way, Ritsu, why is
it you're here, exactly?
I'm sorry! I'm not keeping
you from anything, am I?
Mm-hm!
I'm sorry!
There, there, settle
down. I was just kidding.
You really are just
like your mother.
You know, you'll be
all grown up soon.
You're going to have to learn
to hold yourself together
if you want to make
it on your own.
Y-yes.
I'm sorry.
Oh, but where
are my manners?
I never properly
introduced myself.
I'm Ritsu Sohma and I'm
sorry about earlier.
Oh, no it's okay!
I'm Tohru Honda.
It's very nice
to meet you!
I almost forgot. I have
something I wanted to give you.
[Shigure] Oh, what's
this? Presents?
Yes. I was going to
bring a fruits basket,
but then I didn't really know
what kind everyone liked,
so I brought some
fruit books instead!
I'm sorry. Do you
not like them?
No, they're
just fine.
Aaah! I'm so sorry!
I'm such a terrible guest!
I'll go by some
fruit right away!
Kidding.
Kidding!
It's all right. You
don't have to pretend.
You can tell
me the truth.
I know. I'm not worthy
of visiting your house.
No, that's not
true at all.
No, it's not!
Like I said,
I've been wanting to meet
you for a long time now.
I'm glad
you're here!
Really, I am! It's made me very
happy to finally talk to you.
Thank you. You're
very kind to say that.
Actually, I've been looking
forward to meeting you, too.
Ever since I heard about
you from my mother.
Well, then, I guess we
both have something
to be happy
about!
She's such a pretty
girl when she smiles.
Do we have
a visitor?
It's been a long
time, Yuki.
Sorry for dropping
by unexpectedly.
You haven't changed,
especially the way you dress.
I'm sorry! Forgive me! I'll put
on something else right away!
No. Hasn't
changed a bit.
[Tohru] Ritsu!
Are you okay?
Uh-huh.
Well, in that case, why
don't I make you some tea?
Thank you
very much.
Try to be
nice, Yuki.
It took Ri a lot of
courage to visit us today.
And for a very noble
cause, I might add.
You came all
the way here
just to meet Tohru,
isn't that right?
I guess it has
been a while.
I saw your mother a few months
ago, at the hot spring.
Anyway, how
have you been?
Oh, I've been all right.
How long has it been?
I don't even remember! But
you seem to be doing well.
It's amazing. Since
I saw you last,
you've gotten to look even
more like your brother!
Well, goodbye then.
Oh! What? What did I do?
Did I say something wrong?!
Oh, I've offended him. I
shouldn't be allowed to speak.
Every time I
open my mouth,
I make everyone around
me uncomfortable!
Well, that
is true.
Oh, you're right! I'm the most
annoying person in the world!
I'm sorry I bothered you!
I'll leave right now!
Forgive me! I should
have never stayed so long!
Wait, don't leave yet. I
mean, you just got here,
and you came all this
way and everything.
Besides, I still have
to serve you your tea.
No, please. Don't bother
yourself over me.
I'm not
worth it.
Sure you are! And it's
no bother at all.
Actually, it's my
pleasure! Stay a while!
You've already given me
enough with your kind words.
I couldn't possibly let you
do anything else for me!
No, really!
I want to!
No, really! You
don't have to--
Oh-h no!
Miss Honda?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine, but...
but what about Ritsu?
Ahhh! What
have I done?
What sort of low-life am I,
to destroy my host's property!
Um, I think it
was my fault...
I'm sorry!!!!!!!
I apologize for being
such a terrible guest!
I'll apologize to
the entire universe!
Ritsu!
Watch out!
Huh? Um, why did, uh...
Why did she transform?
I mean, when she's
a girl then...
B-blood!
Blood!
[Yuki]
Miss Honda!
[Tohru] Um, what
just happened?
So, anyway, I
was wondering
if you could come take
a look at Tohru's cut.
That is, when you think
you can spare the time.
Fine. I'll stop by the
house this evening.
Uh? Ah-haa...
What's this, Hatori?
I don't think I've
ever heard you
sound so eager
to come over...
Could it be you have a
secret crush on Tohru?
Ah! I guessed right, didn't I!
You naughty, naughty man, you!
No. I was simply too amazed by
your stupidity to say anything.
So, actually,
Ritsu's a boy.
But for whatever reason, he's
always dressed like a girl
ever since he
was a child.
Oh, so that's what happened.
I really had no idea!
It didn't even occur to
me that he wasn't a girl.
There you go. Not
too tight, is it?
Thanks, it much
better now.
So, why is it that Ritsu
dresses like a girl?
Because he feels more
comfortable that way.
Ri is naturally a
very timid person.
And when he's
dressed like a girl,
he doesn't feel as much
pressure to be assertive.
I suppose that
makes sense.
By the way, did anyone
happen to see where he went?
Oh, dear God,
please punish me.
Send a bolt of lightning
to strike me down!
Oh no, Ritsu!
What are you doing?
Oh my. How did
he get up there?
Oh, Tohru. I know nothing I can
say will change what I've done,
but I am sorry for
injuring you so badly.
No, I'm okay, really!
It was only a scratch!
I also apologize
for not telling you
I was a boy when we
met. I was too ashamed!
No, it's okay!
So he does
know that
dressing like a girl
is strange, after all.
It didn't bother me that you
were wearing girls' clothes!
In fact, I thought you looked
really cute in that dress!
Tohru, I'm not sure that's
really going to help right now.
Ahh... Why? Why am I so stupid?
Why can't I do anything right?
No matter how
hard I try,
I do nothing but cause
trouble wherever I go!
Well, that's certainly
been the case today.
I'm a complete
failure.
At everything I do, I'm
absolutely worthless.
I know this, and
yet I continue
to burden the human
race with my presence.
Every day, I rob the world
of valuable air by breathing.
I'm a thief! And I
hate myself for it!
I don't deserve
to exist!
But even though I know
it's the right thing to do,
I'm such a
useless coward.
I don't even have
the courage to jump!
No! Don't!
Don't jump!
It's okay if you don't
have that kind of courage!
The important thing
is, you're alive.
And life hurts sometimes, and
sometimes it can be hard,
but it won't
always be that way.
There's got to be a
reason for you to live.
[Tohru] Ritsu!
My ankle, I've
twisted it.
So ends that
little adventure.
I'm going
inside.
Um... but... uh...
Shigure told me that
Tohru had been injured,
but he didn't say anything
about you being hurt as well.
I know. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Well, Ha'ri, it's been
a long, strange day.
Now, where
were you hurt?
Oh...
here... See?
I cut my hand, but
it's fine now.
Yuki gave me a bandage, and
really took good care of me.
Did he?
Uh-huh! I didn't realize
Shigure had called you.
I'm sorry to make you come
all the way here for nothing.
But thanks for
thinking about me!
Um... excuse
me, Shigure?
I was just
wondering...
Would you
mind terribly
if I stayed at your
house for the night?
Well, this is
a surprise.
Trying to be more
assertive, are we?
Yes, I'm
trying.
What the hell are Ritsu
and Hatori doing here?
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
It's been three days
since Ritsu came to visit.
I think there's
definitely something
on his mind that's
troubling him,
and a couple times,
it seemed like
he was about to
say something.
But whatever it is, so far
he's kept it to himself.
I hope I put in
enough seasoning.
It's not too
bland is it?
Not at all. It's
quite tasty.
Good, I'm glad
you like it.
She's great,
isn't she?
Yes, I'll bet right
now you're wishing
you had a cute little
housewife of your very own!
You know, you really shouldn't
make such stupid comments.
'Cause I'm gonna knock
you through the roof!
Oh-h, Kyo. I didn't
see you there.
No one's the little housewife
of anyone, got it?!
And if I hear you say it again,
I'm gonna snap you in two!
Help! Kyo is
scaring me!
Bastard.
Well, anyway. Good
morning, Kyo!
And you! You could at least
be a little bit angry!
Oh... Uh...
[Kyo] You shouldn't let
that stupid dog get away
with saying that
stuff all the time!
Settle down, Kyo. Jealousy
is very unbecoming.
It's not like that! So
don't start with me!
Hell, what are you
even doin' here?
Oh, well Hatori's been
looking after Ritsu, you know,
to make sure his ankle's
getting better and everything.
Forget I
asked! Jeez!
Yeah, that's just perfect.
We're out of milk.
Uh... I'm sorry! I
completely forgot!
I'll run out to the store
right now and get some more!
No, I-- you don't
have to do that.
Yes, I do. It's my
responsibility to make sure
we have all the
things we need.
So I should go--
Aaah! I'm sorry! It's
not her fault! It's me!
I'm the one
to blame!
I'm the one who wanted to
have cereal for breakfast!
And I'm the one who
selfishly allowed Tohru
to pour the last of the milk
into my bowl! I'm so sorry!
I'm the
guilty one!
I'm the evil person
who should be punished!
Please! Don't blame
her! Punish me! Aaah!
Oh yeah. he's
still here, too.
I'm sorry! Not only did I come
to Shigure's house uninvited,
but then I was
so bold as to ask
if I could stay
for one night!
Only now I've imposed on
you for three whole days!
And to make
things worse,
Um...
Ritsu?
If you're going to flail
about the kitchen like this,
at least put down
your bowl first.
Here, Kyo. You can take
the rest of the milk
from my cereal.
Please, I insist.
Over my
dead body.
But, what else can I do
to make this up to you?
What do
you think?
You can march down to the
store and buy some more milk!
Wait.
Don't yell.
What's all
the noise?
Oh! Good
morning!
It looks like
someone overslept.
Ah! I'm sorry, I should
have woken you up!
Now you're going to
be late for school,
and it's all
my fault!
Oh, that's
the noise.
You'll be punished
for being tardy!
Possibly expelled
from school!
I'm so sorry! I've
ruined your life!
I thought I taught you
guys this already.
Here. Watch closely.
It's the
magic touch!
I don't even
wanna know.
I think I'm going
back to bed.
You know Ri, you really could
stand to relax a little.
Yes, I'm sorry.
And you don't always have
to apologize for everything.
In fact, that probably causes
more problems than it solves,
especially the
way you do it.
Shigure still hasn't grasped
the concept of 'tact', I see.
To be a more
confident person,
you have to start
acting like one.
That is what you
want, isn't it?
Yes it is, more than
anything in the world!
Someday, I hope to be just
as confident as Ayame!
[Shigure] No.
That's impossible.
You're right. It's
hopeless, isn't it?
Well, I'd say it's
unrealistic at the very least.
When it comes to confidence,
Aya's is off the scale.
I think what
Shigure means is,
it's good to have
a long-term goal,
but it might be
better to start
with more reasonable,
immediate goals.
Just try not to be
too hard on yourself.
Oh, okay.
[Shigure] Well, right! Yes!
That's exactly what I said!
[Hatori] No
it wasn't.
I'm so sorry! So
very, very sorry!
Please! I
beg of you!
I'm sorry. Mommy,
Daddy, I'm so sorry!
Poor
Ritsu.
He has such a
sweet smile.
And I'm so glad
I got to see it,
because I don't think
it happens too often.
Just like Yuki, and Kyo,
and all of the other Sohmas,
he blames himself
for everything
that's happened
in his life.
Why was I ever even
born into this world?
I'm so happy
you're here.
I really am. And
you know, Tohru,
everyday that you're
here with me,
since the first
day you were born,
I have a reason
to smile.
But I'm always here,
silly! You're my mommy!
I was born to
be with you!
Well, I guess that's
why I'm always happy!
No! No! I'm sorry!
Please, forgive me!
I'm sorry I can't give
these to you right now!
I'll come back,
and I'll buy some more
jelly buns just for you!
But these aren't mine! I
have to give them to Shigure!
I'm so sorry! I
apologize to you!
Uh, Ritsu?
So those are
for Shigure?
Uh-huh. He asked me
to pick them up.
He said he just couldn't write
without some fresh jelly buns!
Yeah, that sounds like
something he'd say.
Um!
Yes? Were you going
to say something?
No, no, Tohru, you were
going to say something first.
No, really, I don't mind.
Please, go right ahead.
No, really, that's all
right. After you, please.
Oh, no, I
just couldn't!
Me either!
Um, you know,
for some reason
I don't think this is
really getting us anywhere.
Why don't you go first,
Ritsu? Please, I insist!
O-okay.
I wanted to ask
you something.
Oh?
Um, I was wondering when
you talked to my mother...
Did she say anything to you?
Well, anything bad about me?
I'm sorry. Now I've
made you uncomfortable.
It was wrong of me to ask
a question like that.
Forgive me, please.
It's just I know my
parents are disappointed
to have ever had
a child like me.
Of course, I
understand perfectly
why it is they
feel that way.
I'm the most useless
person I know.
It's bad enough being
born with the Sohma curse,
but I don't have a single
talent to make up for it
like the other
Zodiac members.
I'm not particularly
smart, or athletic.
In everything I do,
I'm average at best.
It's a well-known fact
among the Sohma family,
how useless I am.
It seems my parents
have been apologizing
for me my
whole life.
When I was young I found
that dressing like a girl
made me feel more
comfortable somehow, safe.
But any time I do it, it
only makes my parents
have to apologize
for me even more.
I want to be a more
confident person.
I've tried to stop
dressing like a girl.
But I'm not confident.
I couldn't do it.
I'm a complete failure,
just a worthless coward.
It tears me
apart inside.
I don't want my
mother and father
to have to apologize
for me anymore.
I want them to have a child
that they can be proud of.
A much better
child than me.
I'm sorry.
It might even be better for
them if I wasn't here at all.
And really, there's no good
reason for me to stay.
There's no reason for
my ever being born.
I may have believed that
there was, at one time.
But even if I did,
it's gone now.
Knowing this, how can
I still be so bold
as to burden the world with
my pathetic, useless life?
[Tohru] We're all searching
for a meaning to our lives.
Everyone...
We have to.
Because, no matter
who you are,
I don't think
anyone is born
knowing the reason
why they're here.
It's just something you have
to find as you go along.
And it... it's
different for everyone.
There are as many
reasons to live
as there are people in the
world, maybe even more.
So, the reason
for being born,
the reason you've been
put here in the world,
I think it's something we all
have to find for ourselves.
So we search within
our hopes and dreams,
our work, the people in our
lives, in everything we do.
And even if the reason we
find seems hazy or unclear,
even if it's so tiny that
you can hardly see it,
the important thing is
that you always have one.
As long as I'm alive,
that's what I want,
to have a
reason to go on.
And you know, you
can always find one
if you know
where to look.
The people in my life give
me a reason for living.
I want to live my life for
the people that I care about.
And someday, I hope
I'll find someone
who wants to live
their life for me.
So even when things are
tough, and it's hard to go on,
it makes me want
to try harder.
Because I'm not just living for
me, I'm living for them, too.
And so, I think it's
good that you're bold,
that you're
still here.
'Cause you know,
the world really is
a much better place
with you in it!
Thank you.
I've wanted someone to
tell me those words again.
I needed to hear
them again.
Maybe I will find it, my
reason for living, someday.
And maybe... maybe I can find
it in someone I care about.
I'd like that, to find
someone to live for,
to share my life with.
That would be good.
And when I do find
that special someone,
the first thing we'll
do is eat jelly buns.
I'd like that too, to
find that special person
I can share my life with,
and eat jelly buns.
I want to be able
to say to someone,
"I was born to
be with you."
And maybe, they'll want to
say those words to me, too.
Oh, Shigure must
be wondering
what's taking me
so long, by now.
Uh-huh.
But once we get there,
he's going to be able
to write his whole
novel in a day!
Oh?
Sure! With three
dozen jelly buns,
he'll have plenty
of inspiration!
Oh...
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
[Kazuma] Tonight.
I plan to do it tonight.
And, whatever happens,
I thought I should
warn you in advance.
[Shigure] I see.
So, what led you
to this decision
all of the sudden?
[Kazuma] I think this girl could
open his heart and accept him.
[Shigure] What will
this do to her?
Kazuma? Are you truly prepared
to trust her with everything?
[Kazuma] I wonder if
you might be so good
as to loan me a moment of
your time this evening?
[Tohru] Sure.