I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
[Tohru] Um, As long as I'm
going to be living here,
do you think it
would be all right
if I told two of my
friends where I am?
I'm sure they'll really want
to know... if that's okay.
So long as you don't mention
anything about, you know,
the zodiac and whatnot, I
don't particularly mind...
Thanks
so much!
You see... The Sohma
family has been living
under a secret curse
for generations.
If they're ever hugged by
someone from the opposite sex,
they transform into animals
from the Chinese Zodiac!
It's hard to believe,
but it's true!
And naturally,
this is a secret
they can't allow anyone
to find out about...
What!?
So not only were you
living in a tent,
but now you've moved into
Prince Yuki's house?!
Seriously?!
Yes. I'm sorry for not saying
anything about it sooner.
There was a lot that happened,
but everything's fine now...
And they're all
really nice people.
So there's nothing
to worry about!
This is definitely a bolt out
of the blue... I wonder...
How will the Prince
Yuki Fan Club girls
react when they
hear the news?
I thought it was
strange how you've been
spending so much time talking
to the prince and orange-top
lately... Now I
understand...
Perhaps we should have
them invite us over.
I'd like to
see for myself
whether or not this is
a suitable environment
for you to
be living...
Hey, great idea. Let's
check it out right now.
Wait. If we show
up unexpectedly,
they may not
serve snacks.
Oooh, another good point.
You're two for two.
Okay then... we'll stay
over tomorrow night.
Uh...
wait...
Okay!
High-school girls...
1 -2 -3...
Ahh... I can't help but
wonder what kind of girls
these friends of
Tohru's are...
A Yankee
and a psychic.
Ah...
They're here!
[Tohru] Hi, come in! I guess
you found the house okay.
[Hana] No.
We got lost...
I'm thinking this
was a bad idea.
Just don't do
anything stupid.
That goes double for
you, you damn rat.
Yes... all of us would
do well to be careful
while they're here.
Because I wonder,
if either of these
girls were to find out
about the family curse, what
would happen... do you think?
[Shigure] At
the very least,
I suppose that Tohru would
no longer be allowed
to stay in
this house.
Well, either way...
something's bound to turn out!
Que sera sera.
You just like hearing
yourself talk, don't you?
[Hana]
There's a dog.
Over there.
Oh! Yes,
that's a dog!
[Tohru] So, these
are my friends.
Arisa Uotani and
Saki Hanajima.
Hey.
A pleasure.
Yes, welcome, welcome! Please,
make yourselves right at home.
Say, it's 'Shigure',
right? This is your place?
So what do you do to pay
the rent around here?
Oh-ho, me? I'm a writer...
A novelist, actually.
Did you say
you're a novelist?
Why the heck are
you so surprised?
This is the first
she's heard of it.
Right... I really
I had no idea...
What was it, again? Fine
literature, or something?
Uh-huh... that's right.
This sort of story.
Oh sorry, my mistake...
This is my real work...
This one here was just
something I did for fun.
So that makes it okay for you
to write that dime-store smut?!
You're a sicko,
you know that?!
What were
you thinking...?
Shigure, that's amazing!
I mean, to think
I actually know someone as
important as a novelist!
Careful,
Miss Honda.
You don't want to
inflate his ego too much.
Like his head could
get any bigger
than it
already is...
How wonderful! I just
made another new discovery!
[Shigure] Well,
enough about me.
Why don't you tell us
something about yourselves?
You could start by telling
us how you met Tohru.
What,
serious?
I'm sure we'd all like to
hear! Right Yuki? Right Kyo?
[Tohru]
Uo saved me
Hey, pinhead! You better
not step on those... you!
Wait let me back up... This
one time in middle school,
I dropped all my
notes in the hall...
What have I
done...?
Heh heh... Yeah,
I remember that.
I guess I could get a
little... 'rough' back then.
[Both]
Back then?
Well, you were still a
Yankee then... Weren't you?
Right... I started runnin'
with them in the 5th grade?
You always used to wear
those masks all the time...
And I had my
eyebrows thinned out,
and wore those
long skirts.
[Hana]
You're forgetting,
You do all of those
things now, Arisa.
I guess
you're right.
That's lovely... She's
so... How shall I say it-
by putting it
into words,
I'm afraid the nobility of it
all would only be obscured...
Of what?
You know,
she's so spunky!
You sick
bastard.
How sad... Love,
doomed from the start.
You're
reading that?
That silly little thing?
Oh I'm flattered!
So what do
you think?
You don't want to
know what I think.
Oh... no??
But when is
Volume 2 coming out?
Look, can we just knock it
off with the books? Okay?
Everyone's getting
along so well.
It's so nice
that we can all have a good
time together like this!
I know! I just thought of
something fun we could do!
Wait here,
I'll be right back!
So then... Saki,
you never did tell us
how you and Tohru
got to be friends...
Are you sure you're
ready to hear?
Oh ah... that's okay, as
long as you're friends now!
That's what's
important!
We were in
middle school,
and I was transferred
into Tohru's class...
Ah-h...
is that so?
Yes... You see, at
my previous school,
I had caused something
of a disturbance...
Well, that is a wonderful
story, isn't it.
But I just remembered I
have some work to do,
so if you kids
will excuse me...
He ran off.
Ran the
hell away...
I gotta say, I didn't know
what to make of all this
when she
told us,
but it looks like Tohru's
fitting right in here...
I'm happy
for her...
...and I guess I
can understand
why she didn't want to
say anything at first...
But still...
[Uo] We made
a promise.
The three of us swore
over Kyoko's grave,
that when the
time came,
we would be there to help
each other, no matter what.
[Uo] That probably sounds a
little bit overdramatic.
But it wasn't
really, for us...
After all, Tohru was our first
real friend and everything...
Tohru... Tohru and
Kyoko, both... you see,
they were there for me when
I needed someone most...
Thanks
to them,
I found the strength to climb
my way up out of all the crap
I had fallen into...
They helped me to
believe in myself..
that I could
change if I wanted...
And when I met
the two of them...
for the first time,
I discovered that I
did want to change...
I wanted to be someone
Tohru could be proud
to call
her friend,
the way I was proud
to call her mine...
[Uo] So, this time around, with
everything that's happened...
the fact that I wasn't
there to help Tohru...
...that bothers me.
I mean, that she
would even think
she had to go through all
this trouble by herself...
Maybe she doesn't think
she can count on us...
Or maybe we're just not
that good... as friends...
Nah, I just don't think
she's the kinda' girl
who worries about
stuff like that.
Miss Honda is...
she's the kind of
person who puts others'
well-being
before her own...
Sorry it
took so long...
I hope you're all ready to
play... Rich Man, Poor Man!
[Hana] Ah, that's
a fine idea, Tohru.
[Uo] Okay, how 'bout we pick
it up where we left off?
I don't think I
got to finish
makin' a fool
outta' orange-top here.
[Kyo] Yeah, talk it up!
But this time, when I win,
you have to dye
your hair black!
[Uo] Oh? Well,
when you lose,
you have to bleach all
the dye outta' your hair,
and leave
it white!
[Kyo] It's naturally
this color!
[Hana] Is
that right?
[Kyo]
That's right!
Yuki... Would you like
to shuffle the cards?
Uh..
I...
Sure.
[Uo] Why, you rotten little-
You and your cheap-ass tricks!
[Kyo] Cheap nothin'!
That's fair game!
You're the one
playin' tricks, Yankee!
Next time you pull that crap,
I'm gonna light you up!
Go ahead
and try!
It'll be the dumbest
thing you ever did!
I will take
you out!
Oh yeah, some tough guy!
You're runnin' away!
Who's running?!
I'm going to the bathroom!
Aww...
Gotta take a leak?
What's it
to you?!
Better hurry! We don't
want you to piss yourself!
Dammit, you
got a foul mouth!
[Yuki] Something
wrong, Miss Uotani?
Uh... no...
Ahh. Well,
that's good.
It's just that things
sounded like they were
getting pretty heated
there for a minute...
I know! Until Kyo gets
back from the bathroom,
why don't we all play a
quick game of Sevens!
Yeah...
sure let's play...
Uo!
[Yuki] Miss
Honda, look out!
Tohru...
Are you okay?
Are you
hurt at all?
No... I-
I'm all right.
Ah! You see? I didn't
fall! Just cleaning up!
Scrub, scrub, scrub,
scrub... hehe... see...?
Stupid cat!
Damn rat.
[Uo] Ol' orange top
sure is takin' his time.
[Tohru]
Sure is...
And the prince just up
and disappeared, I guess...
You're right. I wonder where
our kind hosts have run off to.
[Uo] For
the love of...
we can't even start this
game of Sevens, you know?
A cat...
Oh! You're playing
Sevens, right...?
That sounds like fun! Think
you have room for one more?
Well if it isn't the
master novelist...
You any good
at this game?
Well, you
should know,
in the old days they used to
call me The Sevens Bandit.
Oh? Really?!
That's incredible!!
I'll say.
It's a lie.
But enough
about me!
Let's get to playing, shall
we? So what are the rules?
You guys hear that? Sounded
like some kinda' 'boom'.
[Hana] There was a
definite, 'boom'.
This is not good! I think Kyo
just changed back to normal!
Unless we do something, those
two are going to see him.
And what's worse,
he'll be naked!
I know! For now, I'll
throw him Yuki's clothes!
Maybe no one
will notice...
It doesn't matter.
Anything to cover him up!
Kyo!
Catch this, Kyo!
Huh...? Why
is this so heavy?
Ahh! I thought
you'd run away!
I'm so glad you're
back! Uh, um, Spot.
Spot?!
That's odd... It appears
we've run out of snacks...
I'll go find
the kitchen.
Oh, no! Kyo
just changed back,
and the idiot's already
transformed again! Okay!
I've got to
cause a diversion.
Now Yuki, too?!
That's weird...
I swear I thought I saw
orange-top in here...
Miss Honda... I
think Spot is trying
to tell us he's
hungry, don't you?
Yeah... That must be
it! Here! C'mon boy!
Let's go into
the kitchen, Spot!
Tohru, wait.
Uh... yes?
Some more snacks?
If you don't mind.
Oh! Sure!
I'm really
sorry...
I promise, the last thing
I wanted was for this
to cause everybody
so much trouble...
Hey, nuffin' to
abologishe for.
I'm not
so sure...
Tohru, if these people
are important to you,
then they're important to us
too... Do you understand?
Yes. I understand.
Thank you.
Oh, but I'm sure Yuki's
wondering where we are...
Come on...
This game isn't going
very well... now is it?
Uh... Why don't I-?
I'll go check on her...
Sorry to keep
you waitin-
Miss
Honda!!
Oh no, Yuki!
H- help!
Eh? But you're mixed in
with all of the jelly buns.
I can't tell
where you are!
Here,
Miss Honda!
Where... ?
Where are you?
Here!
Let's see... jelly bun...
jelly bun... jelly bun, uh...
Ah!! Yuki,
it's you!
Wait! Miss Honda,
that's a...
...a jelly bun!!
Hey-y! Tohru,
nice catch!
Although, most of
them still fell.
Maybe I was lucky
she didn't catch me.
She squeezed that bun so hard,
all the filling came out!!
I thought we might at least
find something to wear in here.
So it's
empty, then?
Yeah. Tohru is rather thorough
about doing the wash.
Aww, hell with it!
Just let 'em see us!
All we gotta do is erase
those girls' memories
and we'll be
fine, right?
I suppose that's true, as
long as you're okay with that.
Okay with what?
It would mean Tohru's memory
would have to be erased as well.
Stay here! I'm gonna
get us some clothes!
Arisa...
You're about
to step on...
[Uo] Yeah?
Step on what?
[Hana] An orange cat, with
clothes tied around its neck...
...being carried in the mouth
of a dog... who went that way.
A-one-two, one-two,
one-two, one-two...
You know, nothing gets
the blood flowing
like a rubdown
with a dry towel!
A-one-two, one-two,
one, two, one-two...
Idiot.
This is
a fine bed.
Isn't it? Shigure
bought it for me.
Well... from
the looks of it,
he must really
think big of you, huh?
That's exactly
how it appears.
As long as
he's at it,
this room could
probably use some more,
you know,
girl stuff.
Like right here.
You should have him put
in a dressing table,
or something
like that.
Oh, no, I
couldn't!
I couldn't think
about wanting more!
I'd be asking
for it! Really...
I mean, I've only
just started to realize
how lucky a person I am to have
so much already, you know?
[Shigure] Tohru, if these
people are important to you,
then they're important to
us too... Do you understand?
I have a new home, living
here with the Sohmas...
And I have the two
most wonderful friends
in the whole world, who
care about me so, so much...
Just knowing that I can
always count on you
to be there for me, and how
much strength that gives me...
I'm already so lucky.
If I'm not thankful
for what I have,
I'd just be
asking for it!
I love
you both.
Nah, I just don't think
she's the kinda' girl
who worries about
stuff like that.
Miss Honda is... she's
the kind of person
who puts others' well-being
before her own...
I guess they do understand
her. Pretty well, I'd say...
That they do... Tohru
is that kind of girl.
Invincible love.
That's right.
Right...
Uh... Hey,
Yuki... Are you-??
So, Yuki. You're having a
hard time waking up as usual...
Yeah, yeah, just
keep movin' will ya'...
[Tohru] Wow, Kyo. With as much
as you want to beat Yuki,
you still don't try to sneak
up on him when he's like this.
It's very
admirable.
No, that's not it.
It's not like that.
He's stronger when
he's half-asleep.
Ah, so you have tried
to attack him, then?
Yeah, I tried! And
I got beat even worse
than when
he's awake Okay?!
Do you know
what that means?!!
It means that stupid,
dirty little sissy rat-boy
is always
holding back on me!
What gives?! I thought
you were still out of it!
Your stupid
voice woke me up.
Fine! I don't care
anymore... dammit!
Asleep or not, it's
you and me! Right now!
I'm gonna mop up this
kitchen with your face!
How can you even talk
about this nonsense
so early
in the morning?
A cat
and mouse...
That's what
they're like.
You think?
The way they're...
fighting,
it's like a
cat and mouse...
Just like the ones
in the old cartoon.
Yeah... Something
or other and Jerry.
That's right!
These guys are still here!
So, the two of you don't
get along too well, do ya'?
I suppose not...
Even so, this seems like
a pleasant enough house...
Which is good, because if it
had been a poor environment
for Tohru to
be living in...
There are many things I would
have to do to correct it.
Yes...
Many things.
What... kind of
'many things'?
But I can see that
the two of you...
You both have fine
electric signals...
[Hana] Oh, you didn't know?
That's even better, I think.
Well, I'm sure you'll
do your best to be nice...
To Tohru,
we mean.
Oh, Uo...
Hana...
[Uo] We'll come by for
another visit soon.
Yes, let's...
I'm curious to
learn more about
the Soma Family's
unique signals.
Okay! Now how
'bout some breakfast?
Yes, breakfast.
Hey, hey hey! You
gotta be kidding!
Damn girls
are takin' over!
I- I know it must seem that
way! But, they mean well...
You'll see!
Uo and Hana are both really,
really good people!
So, please...
Fine.
Whatever.
Afterall, they are
your friends, right?
Right!
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
[Kyo] I say we make it
a rice ball battle!
[Yuki] Hmm... what if we did
something like a hit n' miss?
[Tohru] The Cultural
Festival is about to begin.
You're both looking well...
Yuki... Kyo
[Hana] Strange boy...
[Uo] Yeah... Like
you're one to talk.
You're pretty strange
yourself, y'know.
[Tohru] When someone is
jealous of someone else,
it's probably
because they can see
the pickled plum in the
middle of their back.
[Kyo] There's one stuck to your
back too... a plum I mean.