I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
Hey, it's
me, Tohru!
If you remember, last
month for Valentine's Day,
I saved up to buy chocolates
for all of my friends.
It wasn't much, but I wanted
to give them something
to say thank you for everything
they'd done for me...
So yesterday, I really
wasn't expecting Momiji
to give me a
White Day present--
especially not an all-
expenses-paid trip
to a
hot spring!
But that's
what he did!
And here we
are now--
on our Super Relaxing
Hot Spring Steam Trip!
[Momiji] Hey, Tohru!
Look! A mountain!
[Tohru]
Ah, yes.
Ooh! And
a river!
Uh-huh...
And a
field!
Uh-huh...
And look! It turned out
to be a beautiful day, huh?
Yes, it did!
Right Yuki?
Right Kyo?
[Both]
I guess...
So why are you guys
being so quiet?
You're not sad you
came, are you?
Oh, I
hope not...
especially since you only
came to keep me company...
and... well, thank
you for that...
But I hope I'm not taking
away from anything important.
I mean, if there were other
things you had planned...
Ah... forget
about it...
I only came because
there wasn't anything
better to do
at home...
Oh...
okay...
And I haven't been to the
hot spring in a long time...
I was happy
to come along.
Oh, I
get it.
You were just thinking
how nice it's gonna be
once we get
there... Right?
Mm-hm.
Then it's settled!
Once we get there...
We're all gonna try to have
as much fun as we can!
Right Tohru?
Uh-huh! Right! I'm sure
that won't be hard to do.
I'm already having
such a wonderful time!
I never dreamed
giving out Valentines
would mean I'd be
whisked away to a place
as fancy as
a hot spring!
And, not
only that...
That I'd get
to ride there
in the comfort of a private
charter bus like this...
It all seems too
good to be true.
Like I'm a princess
in a fairy tale!
Tohru can be the princess,
and I'll be her prince!
Ah, give me a break...
It's just a hot spring...
It's nothin' you gotta
get all worked up over.
I think it's
just ahead...
[Tohru] Wow... It's
absolutely beautiful!
[Momiji] Well, come on Princess
Tohru, your room awaits!
Ah... Thank you, Momiji.
It's all so wonderful...
You really have made me
feel like a princess...
That's right!
You're the princess!
Ooh! And I'll
be your knight!
[Kyo] Knock
it off.
Well then, I'll be back
to pick you up tomorrow.
Okay. Thank
you! Bye-bye!
Oh... thank goodness,
I'm so glad you're here...
Oh... don't worry. She's
the Hot Spring Lady...
The word is
'hostess'...
Uh-h, a-are you okay?
Is everything all right?
Pleeease! Let me
show you to your room!
Guess what! The Hot
Spring Lady is a Sohma, too!
But she gets sick a
lot, so she stays here,
for the health
benefits and all that.
The Sohmas own
this place, you know.
[Tohru]
Oh, really?
I apologize if
I startled you...
Oh, no... please, you don't
have to apologize to me...
just as long as
you're feeling okay,
that's what's
important...
You are too kind to an old
woman like me... but thank you.
I'm surprised
Young Master Shigure
didn't accompany
you today.
Perhaps he was too
busy with work?
'Young Master Shigure'?
How old are you?!
Yes, he had deadlines
on two books coming up.
Well,
that's a shame.
You see, you're the only
guests we have today...
It would have been a fine
chance to visit with him...
So, if she's a Sohma, and
if she already knows
Shigure and Yuki
and everyone...
I wonder if that means she
knows about the Zodiac curse?
Or maybe it means she's
one of the members
of the
Zodiac, herself!
Ah, here we are. This
will be your room.
Wow, it's
so big!
[Hostess] Yes. I made sure we
had our best room prepared
for your
arrival.
Tohru! Come over here! You've
got to look at this garden!
Wo-ow! I can't believe
how beautiful it all is!
How big is it? It looks
like it goes on forever!
Well... almost... See,
from that forest over there,
all the way to that mountain-
it's all Sohma property!
Really? It all belongs
to your family?
Uh-huh! Everything
you see!
Well... while
we're here...
maybe it would be fun
to go out for a walk.
You wouldn't be the
first to think so...
Actually, we've even had
a few guests go walking
who never
made it back...
Tohru... you were
supposed to laugh.
Oh, that was just a joke...
How silly, of course it was...
Yeah, so
don't worry.
Really, they never lose
the guests for too long...
There's a professional search
party on call at all times.
What?! You mean they have
to send out search parties?!
Tohru, that was
a joke too...
Oh, I guess it
was, wasn't it...
Miss Tohru, I've
prepared a room for you
adjacent to the young
masters' here...
Oh, okay.
Hey!
I hope you don't think I'm
stayin' in the same room
as that
damn Yuki!
You two get along as
poorly as ever, I see...
But please,
don't be upset...
There are sliding doors
to divide the room...
That's not the point! The point
is, I didn't come here to--
The point is, you
just want to stay
in the same room as
Tohru, don't you?
How crude.
Hey! I didn't
say that!
So shut up, Momiji,
you and your damn mouth!
Master
Kyo...
Ahhhh! You should be
ashamed of yourself!
To think you would
even suggest the idea
of sharing a room
with a young woman!
And all this time,
even if you are a cat,
I thought you to be
a decent young man!
Since when have you gotten such
lecherous ideas in your head?!
[Kyo] Hey! Hold
on a minute!
I'm sorry, world!
I must apologize
on behalf of this
dirty-minded boy!
Okay, fine! I'll stay
in the room with Yuki!
Ha ha! Pervert!
Kyo's a pervert!
I think she's stronger
than she lets on...
All right then... I'll leave
you to enjoy yourselves.
Finally.
It's quiet.
There's still
time before dinner,
so let's take a
bath! Okay, Tohru?
Okay!
Let's take
it together!
Okay.
You little- Now
who's the pervert?
Aww-ww,
what'd I do?
Oh... but Momiji is
still so little and all,
I think it'll be
okay. I mean, uh--
Little!? What the hell
are you talking about!?
Miss Ho--
Kyo-o! I wanna go
in with Toh-ruu!!
I wanna! I
wanna! I wanna!!
Wahhh!
Momiji...
Why don't we give Miss
Honda some time to herself?
After all, the reason
we brought her here
was to give her a
chance to relax, right?
Right,
I get it.
But tonight we'll
sleep together, okay?
[Both] He
doesn't get it.
How nice, my first
open-air bath!
And the spring seems
almost big enough
for someone like
Momiji to swim in!
He is
swimming.
Okay... let's
see now...
Ta-da!!
What do you think,
Mom? How's the water?
It feels good,
doesn't it?
I'm doing
that again!
[Kyo] Momiji! Just
get in and be quiet!
Tohru! How
are you doing?
You little brat! Didn't I
tell you to be quiet?!
Aw-w, but Tohru's all by
herself! She's lonely!
Oh, hey! I know! Tohru,
let's sing a song, okay?
That way, it'll seem like
we're all in here together,
and it'll be a lot
of fun! Really!
Uh... A-
a song?
Yeah, yeah!
Sing something!
Well... I wouldn't
know what to sing.
I'm afraid I don't
really know many songs...
Okay, I'll
sing then!
♪ Who's in the
forest, strolling? ♪
♪ The birds and the
bees sing, Momiji! ♪
♪ The frogs in the
pond are calling
Momiji, yes
it's true! ♪
♪ The trees raise
their leaves-- ♪
What the hell
is that?
It's my song.
I made it up!
So why don't you
make up something
that isn't
so annoying?
Just sing it!
Tohru, you sing too!
♪ Who's in the
forest strolling? ♪
♪ The birds and the bees
sing, Momiji! ♪ Your turn!
♪ Who's in the
forest strolling?
The birds and the
bees sing, Momiji! ♪
♪ The frogs in the
pond are calling,
[Yuki] Why frogs,
out of curiosity?
[Kyo] Hey, knock
it off, already!
♪ The frogs in the
pond are calling,
Momiji, yes
it's true! ♪
[Kyo] Ah! This is
driving me crazy!
♪ Who's in the
forest strolling? ♪
♪ The birds and the
bees sing, Momiji! ♪
♪ The frogs in the
pond are calling,
Momiji, yes
it's true! ♪
♪ The trees raise
their leaves together, ♪
♪ Who needs the sun
when we've got you? ♪
♪ Who's in the
forest strolling? ♪
♪ The birds and the
bees sing, Momiji! ♪
♪ The frogs in the
pond are calling,
Momiji, yes
it's true! ♪
Ah, Miss Tohru?
What
happened?
Oh, good. I'm glad to
see you've come around.
It's not very often someone
faints during their bath...
but our
hot spring...
well, it can make
some people dizzy...
Where's
my Mom?!
Here... Do you mean this
photograph? It's alright.
The plastic you
wrapped it in
kept it nice and dry.
No harm done...
Thank
goodness!
Um... but I guess
I really should be
thanking you
for helping me.
I'm sorry if I put
you to any trouble...
Outrageous! Never
in all my years
has a guest
apologized to me-e-e!
Ahh! I should have warned
you it was possible
to get dizzy in
the hot spri-i-ng!
Clearly, I have failed in
my duties as your hostess!
Dig my grave now, so
I may crawl in and die!
I'm so-rry!
I'm so-rr-yy!
Oh, uh...
I beg
your pardon.
N- Not
at all...
So that's a
special photo?
Oh... yes,
it is...
It's a picture
of my mother...
She, well, she passed
away last year...
Oh...
So since she can't
be here herself,
I still wanted her to enjoy
the hot springs... in spirit.
Oh my... What a
beautiful story...
Tohru! Are
you okay?
Oh! Yes I'm fine!
Nothing to worry about!
Really, thank you so much
for all of your help.
[Tohru] Ohh wow!
Incredible!
I've never seen so
many delicious foods
all on
one table!
[Kyo] You think we
can eat all this?
Well, I guess I better get
started serving the rice!
No you don't! You're the
princess today, Tohru.
Remember!
I'll do it!
O- okay.
Here,
Tohru!
Uh... Thank
you, Momiji...
Don't you think that's
a little bit much--
What the hell
was that?!
Princess Tohru
gets to go first!
Well, Miss Honda, what
are you going to try?
I don't know...
there's just so much!
Don't be
shy! Dig in!
Oh, I'm just not used
this much attention!
And with all of this
pressure to pick something,
I can't decide!
But they're all waiting
on me, so... uh...
Uh, how about
this one?
It's delicious!
Wonderful. I'm
glad you like it.
Well, go on!
Eat up! Eat up!
Pardon the
intrusion.
But the head chef would
very much like to
pay his respects to
the young masters.
As always, it is my
pleasure to serve you.
Does the cuisine
meet with your approval?
Oh, yeah.
It's even more delicious
than I remembered.
It is! A meal
fit for a king!
Please,
make way!
Ah! It's
too cold!
Nnnnoooo! This
is inexcusable!
I thought I had seen to it
that the young masters' cuisine
would be served with
the hot foods hot
and the cold
foods cold!
Only my complete lack of
competence as a chef
could allow such a lukewarm
dish to be served to you!
I beg your
forgiveness!
May I be cut into a thousand
pieces for this egregious act!
No! It was
my fault!
I clearly waited too
long to serve your meal!
No, it was
my fault!
It was
--No, it
was mine!
By any chance,
are those two...?
...related? Yes.
They're cousins...
It's amazing the
family resemblance.
Ahh... The steam
looks so nice.
And it's such a
beautiful night...
I know! As long
as I'm here,
I'll try going out
for another bath!
Only this time, I'll be
a little bit more careful,
so I don't get
dizzy again...
Exclusively for guests
prone to dizziness
That was nice of
them to set this up...
Here.
I hope that's not too
uncomfortable, Mom...
I just don't want to
take another chance
of getting
you wet.
You know, it's better to
be safe than sorry, right?
My, my...
Oh...
hello.
I see you discovered the
sign I posted... Very good...
You should find this bath
a bit more to your liking...
Ah. And once again, you're
here with your mother.
You are truly a special
young lady, Miss Tohru.
Oh... I don't
know about that.
Now that we have
a quiet moment,
I've been meaning
to speak to you...
Did you know that my own child
is a member of the zodiac,
like Master Yuki
and the others?
Yes, my child was born
under the sign of the monkey.
So when I first heard the
news that you had come
to live among
the Sohmas...
I must admit... It made
me somewhat uneasy...
I was afraid that allowing
an outsider to learn
the secret of the
zodiac curse...
would only lead to greater
suffering for my child,
and all of the other young
masters as well... you see?
However, I'd like to
apologize to you now
for having ever
thought that.
Having met you, Miss Tohru...
I'm no longer worried.
Because if your paths
should cross someday,
I am confident you will be
as much a friend to my child
as you have to
Masters Yuki and Kyo...
Uh-huh!
The monkey... Oh, I do hope
we get to meet someday soon...
Yeah, that's right. The Hot
Spring Lady is Ritsu's mom.
Sorry, I guess I thought
I told you that already.
Oh, so...
Ritsu?
Mm-hm! But enough
about that!
Come play ping-pong
with me, okay?
Kyo and Yuki never let
me play with them...
Out again.
I told you, you have to
let it bounce on the table.
Shut up! That's stupid! Why
would I wanna hit that slow?
Why? Because those
are the rules.
Out again...
Hang in there,
Kyo! You can do it!
I thought at
least at ping-pong
he might have a
chance to beat me...
but as usual,
he's hopeless.
How can I beat you with
all these stupid rules!
You damn rat!
How 'bout we
take this outside?!
You know, you're the
one who wanted to play
this game in the
first place...
Uh... well, in that case...
if you still want to,
I'll try playing
with you...
Ooh, that sounds like
fun! Play her, play her!
Advance
warning...
I'm not gonna go easy on you
just 'cause you're a girl.
Oh,
right.
Don't forget-
it has to bounce.
You shut up!
I missed it!
Yeah, I noticed.
You kinda' suck...
[Momiji] Kyo, don't
tell her that!
So you think you're
any better than she is,
you little
runt? Huh?
I'll play you
if you want!
All right,
let's go!
Ya-aye!
I serve
first!
Okay!
You asked
for it!
Yuki? Is there
something wrong?
You seem upset,
all of a sudden...
Funny...
That was funny... Miss
Honda that was hilarious...
The way you swung
and missed...
Oh, you're
awful...!
I'm sorry...
It's okay to laugh...
You don't have to hide it.
You could have laughed
in front of us.
Oh, no... I
just couldn't...
If Kyo saw me, I'd
never live it down...
I mean, I've never
even laughed like this
in front of
my parents,
if you can
believe that...
Ah, that was
a good laugh...
Oh, I
almost forgot.
Here...
for you.
It's a
gift.
I'd hoped I'd have a chance
to give it to you earlier,
but somehow the timing just
never seemed to be right...
It's my White Day
present, to you.
Thank you
very much.
I had a hard time deciding
what to get you at first...
...but when I
saw this, it...
well, it just
seemed to suit you...
I do hope you find it to
your liking... Princess.
Uh...
yes... Yes!
Of course I like it...
Really... Thank you so much...
Princess...
...I can think of
no higher honor.
I'm just
kidding...
Sometimes, he really
does seem like a prince...
Tohru!
Oh, Mom, there are
so many princes
in the Sohma family,
not just Yuki...
Yes... Handsome,
lovely, kind princes...
I'm so grateful that I've
gotten to spend this time
together
with them...
Every
minute of it.
Tonight, I think
I really must be
the luckiest girl
in the world...
I'm so thankful...
For everything.
I'm afraid it's
time to say goodbye.
But please... all of you... I
do hope you'll come again soon.
Do you have to lean
on me like that?
Thank you. And take
care of yourself.
You as well... You
as well, Miss Tohru...
O-kay.
Heavy.
Okay.
I think our
driver got lost.
Hey,
Momiji...
I guess after this I won't get
to see you for a while, huh?
Huh?
But you know, I don't
think I even know
what year you'll be starting
in school this spring...
Is this your first
year of middle school?
Nope!
This spring will be my
first year in high school!
And as it
turns out,
I'll be going to the
same high school as you!
That's right!
Me and Haru, both!
Why you
sneaky little-
Why didn't you
tell us sooner
you and Haru were
coming to our school?!
We wanted it
to be a surprise!
Miss Honda... I'm
guessing you didn't know.
But Momiji actually is only
a year younger than us,
the same
age as Haru.
All this time I thought he
was in elementary school...
And now he's coming
to our high school?
Together with
Hatsuharu!!
Ah-h-h... I don't
even know which part
I should be most
surprised about!
Be surprised
about everything!
[Tohru] Well... I guess,
starting this spring,
high school is going to get
a lot more interesting...
Well, here it is. My White
Day present for Tohru.
Lovely...
isn't it?
The poor girl's
gone far too long...
without suitable clothing to
wear while cleaning the house.
It's amazing no one's
locked you up yet.
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
[Tohru] Spring is
in full bloom,
and it's the first day
of a new school year!
[Uo] Hm... so there's more
Sohmas coming to school, huh?
Go get
them Kyo.
[Hana] Yes, go
get them.
[Kyo] Why me? Why don't you
get her to do it?!
[Momiji] Waaah! Kyo's
picking on me!
[Kyo] Idiot! What the
hell are you doing
wearing a
girl's uniform?!
[Haru] It's okay, isn't it?
It looks good on him.
[Momiji] I heard
he's gonna be here...
Akito...
[Tohru] Akito...?
[Akito] And you must
be, Tohru Honda...