I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
Is he really Prince
Yuki's cousin?
I'll bet he knows
everything about him!
Leave me alone!
Amazing!
Poor Kyo...
Hey.
What were you trying to prove,
pulling a stunt like that.
Think. If you act
like an idiot
I'm the one who's going
to hear about it.
Serves you right...
Why do you wanna go to a school
with all these crazy,
giggling
girls, anyway?
I suppose you'd prefer
I lived my life
in fear of being transformed?
You sound like Akito.
He thought I should attend an
all-boys academy too...
Which is why I
came here.
To get away from him,
and out of that house.
What do you know...? You're
a spoiled little rat.
[Kyo] You want out?
Fine! But as for me...
I'm gonna prove it once and for
all that I'm better than you.
And then I'm gonna take my place
as a true member of this family!
I'm not gonna be
left out any more!
Do you hear me, rat boy?!
No!
I am so sorry...
But I saw what was going on,
and I guess I just panicked...
I'm sorry that
you're angry,
but fighting at school
isn't a good idea!
You'll get into huge
trouble if they catch you!
(And on your first day.. I
didn't think...)
Shut up.
Who do you think you are!
This is between me and him!
It's got nothing to do with
you, you stupid little girl!
From now on, just stay
the hell away from me!
Okay, that was
maximum rage...
He hates me. That's all there
it to it. He really hates me.
You truly are
an idiot.
So what? You're
gonna hit me now?
Wouldn't it hurt
more if I didn't?
[Tohru]
I remember,
when I first heard the story
of the Zodiac animals,
all I could think about
was the poor cat.
While all the other animals
were having a wonderful time
at the banquet, the cat was
still lying in its bed,
dreaming of a party that
would never come...
I know, I won't be a dog
anymore! I'll be a cat, too!
And I really
meant it...
I wanted to show the
cat that, no matter what,
he had a friend...
I liked cats
so much...
I know I would have
been the first to join
a Year of the Cat fan club
if there was such a thing...
But now he hates me..
I'm such a fool, Mom...
A real fool.
Incoming. Tohru's
electric signals.
There
she is...
Hey, what are you doing
kneeling in the hall?
Class is-uh?
I can't believe I
did it again...
I bumped
my head!
That almost hurts more
than the first time!
Look, I'm crying
it hurt so bad!
I would worry,
but I don't think her brain
damage can get any worse...
[Shigure] So, you're home. Had
enough school for one day, huh?
I don't wanna live in
this house anymore.
If you can train on
a mountain for four months,
I think you can endure more
than three days here...
I said such terrible
things to her... Terrible.
And by, her... I take
it you mean Tohru?
Let me guess...
You lost your temper and
yelled at her again, right...?
You know you
shouldn't do that
if you're just going
to regret it...
Not too bright,
now is it?
Save your breath..
I'm just not meant to get
along with other people.
Period. End
of story.
Oh sure, some people
just aren't...
but you're not
one of them.
You lack experience,
that's all.
For example..
I'm sure you could smash
this table to bits
with your
bare hands...
But I'm equally sure you
could punch the table
without breaking it...
And why is that?
Because I know your
training has taught you
to control
your fists.
At least I
should hope so,
after four months of fighting
bears and whatnot...
I didn't
fight bears!
My point - is it takes
just as much training
to get along
with people...
Only, training by
yourself in the mountains
won't do you
any good.
You need to surround
yourself with others.
As you get to
know them,
of course you
take a chance
that you'll end
up hurting them,
or that they'll end
up hurting you.
And one of those things
may very well happen.
But that's the
only way we learn.
About others,
and ourselves.
You're a black belt
in martial arts,
but I'd guess you've still got
a white belt in social skills..
Some day, you're
going to meet someone
who truly wants to be your
friend, and you theirs...
But if you don't
keep training,
you won't be ready
when that happens.
It'll never
happen, anyway.
Ahh, never
say never.
Okay, fine.
Maybe..
if I meet someone with brain
damage.. or something...
That's
the spirit.
I'm home!
Ah, so you are. Is
Tohru not with you?
She had to work
this evening,
but she'll be
done by eleven.
I'm thinking about
picking her up.
That's probably a
good idea..
There are some real
weirdoes around here...
Another day's work, over and
done... But it's late.
I wonder if anyone's
still awake...?
I hope Kyo at least
got some dinner
tonight, if he wasn't too
angry to eat again...
Maybe I could...
oh, but I'm probably the last
person he wants to see...
Just stay the hell
away from me!
Ahh, no one's
ever hated me before.
I don't know
what to do!
Just be yourself.
You'll be fine...
Yes, you're
right Mom!
I just have to
keep trying!
Wh- what was that? Is
there somebody else here?
Oh no!
What if it's one
of those weirdoes
Shigure warned
me about?!
No!!
Kyo! He's going to think
I thought he was a stalker!
Oh, but I guess I did! But I
can't tell him that! Ahh..
Uh, wait... I'm sorry,
it was an accident!
I was just stretching
my arm, and oops!..
Funny how things like
that that happen, huh?
But hey, it's
nice to see-
Quit babbling! If you've got
something to say, say it!
Kyo...
What?!
Uh... I don't know
what to say...
Then don't say
anything!!
I'm sorry!
No, don't be.. Say or don't
say whatever you want...
And, you don't have to-
you know, stay away,
I- Ahh, just hit me
again if you're angry...
I think...
Is he...?
he's trying to apologize
for this morning, isn't he?
Maybe that's why he came
out here to meet me...
So... does that mean-the
other day after school...
I think he was trying to
apologize to me then, too...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry if I gave
you the wrong idea.
I only hit you because I
thought you were a stalker!
Oh. Great.
So you see, it wasn't
because I'm mad at you!
That's not
it at all!
In fact, I
really like you!
I've always liked
the cat from the Zodiac!
What I mean is.. I hope..
maybe.. we can be friends?
[Shigure] Some day,
you're going to meet someone
who truly wants to
be your friend...
What are you
supposed to be?
Some Year of the
Cat Fan Club?
C'mon... Let's
go back.
I think I understand Kyo a
little bit better now.
He doesn't always
mean to get angry.
Sometimes, it's
just hard for him
to say how he
really feels...
But, deep down, I believe
he truly is a nice person,
even though he tries to
hide it most of the time.
[Shigure] Kyo, I hear you
gave Tohru a little scare
while you were out
prowling around last night...
Kyo's a stalker!
You are so
full of it!
And you!
Next time you need
someone to walk you home..
don't look
at me!
That's okay.
Anyway, I'd much rather see
you here at the table
like this
more often...
I'm glad
you're eating.
How do you
like the food?
What do
you want?
Nothing.
You were
staring at me!
No. Just
looking.
Well, I guess there's a
first time for everything!
Do you
like it?
No, I
don't!-
Hey, why don't we play
Rich Man-Poor Man?
Ah, play it with that damn
Yuki.. I don't wanna.
Running away from a
challenge. What are you?
Some kinda' sissy?
Fine! I'll play
your stupid game!
Just don't cry when
you lose, Yankee...
How about
this...
The loser cleans the entire
classroom by himself.
Ahh, aren't those the
most wonderful signals?
Let's ask Yuki if he
wants to play too!
Yuki! Want to play
Rich Man-Poor Man?
You're not here!
I'm sorry...
I'm just not ready to be in a
relationship right now.
So... I think it
would be best if-
No, don't
say it! Yuki!
Uh.. I'm..
sorry?
It's just that... You
were always so nice, I...
You really don't want
to get close to anyone,
do you Yuki?
You shut everyone out,
like you think you're
better than they are...
So what,
I guess a normal
girl like me
just isn't good enough
for you, is that it?
Revolution!
You cheater!
What kinda cheap-ass tricks
are you trying to pull?!
Whatta' you mean tricks?!
Those're the rules!
Let's see..
'Revolution' makes all the
high cards low, right?
Wait... Reverse
Revolution.
You've had
it now, Kyo!
Go for
it Hana!
How embarrassing!
Getting beat by a girl!
Aw, stick it... C'mon!
Let's play again!
You really don't want to get
close to anyone, do you Yuki?
Rich Man-Poor Man...
I know
the rules,
but I can't say I've ever
actually played the game...
Uo just taught me how to
play not too long ago.
It really is
a lot of fun!
You should play
with us next time!
So, it looks like Kyo was
the loser today, was he?
Yes, but I'll still
help him clean up.
No. A loss
is a loss.
You sure?
Don't worry about it.
I'll win next time...
Just like I'll
win against you!
Wait, wait. I think I've
heard this one before...
No joke,
ass-hole!
I am going to beat
you! That's a promise!
I wish
you'd stop
making your inferiority
complex my problem.
I swear, every time you open
your mouth it pisses me off!
And every time you open yours
you sound like an idiot.
[Tohru] They're
fighting again...?
They can't even be in the
same room together, can they?
I guess cats and rats aren't
supposed to get along, really.
But the way
they fight?
There's got to be a
better explanation...
...And then I'm
gonna take my place
as a true
member of this family!
Do you think- maybe...
what he meant by that was,
he's trying to beat Yuki...
because he thinks then he'll
be accepted into the Zodiac?
If that's true,
then that means...
the cat will be included
with the other twelve animals!
That would
be wonderful!
I'm gonna break your
pretty-boy face!
But..
I don't think fighting is the
best way to go about it...
Umm, you guys?
Let's go!
Right now!
Ugh, I can't even
stand to look at you.
Yuki...
Damnit, Why can't I ever kick
him in the head for a change?
But he really tried to
lay me out today...
He must be in a bad
mood or somethin'.
I don't know. I guess it's
because Yuki's always so..
polite, you wouldn't think
he ever had a bad day.
But if what Kyo
said was true,
he might just be keeping
his real feelings
locked up
inside...
Hey, go
check it out.
There's a real looker
standing out front.
I don't remember
the last time
I saw such a pretty face
like that on a boy...
Oh-listen to you. You
just don't quit, do you?
I wonder
if that's...
Yuki!
Hi there. So are
you all finished?
Yes, but don't tell me you
came all the way down here
just to
pick me up.
Sure I did...
It's not too safe for you to
be walking alone at night.
An escort, two
nights in a row...
I have to say,
you and Kyo sure know how
to make a girl feel special!
Well, we
should go...
W- Wait.
Yuki.
Umm.. I hope I'm
not prying, but
if there's something
that's bothering you,
you know you can talk to
me about it if you want...
I'm sorry,
it's just that anytime I ever
had anything on my mind
that was bothering me, it
always made me feel better
to talk about
it with some-
Hey, lovebirds!
Go home!
It's too late for you
kids to be on the street!
Sounds like it's past
your bedtime, too.
What, are you kidding?
It's still early!
But then again,
you don't have to-
I wouldn't want to
talk to me either
if I kept turning
me into a rat.
No. It's not your fault.
I'm the one with the curse.
For years,
living at Sohma House
felt like living in a cage.
Akito always liked to keep
me as far away from...
well, everyone
as he could.
But what I wanted, was
to live a normal life,
with normal
people.
I wanted to move
in with Shigure,
enroll in
this school...
I wondered why he let me go,
at first... I soon found out.
I could leave the house, but
leaving the cage, heh...
that wasn't
so easy.
No. I'm
still a Sohma.
And no matter how
much I might want to,
that's something
I can never change...
I'll always be.. different. I
know that. What scares me is,
if I get too
close to someone,
they might realize that
too... Not like Kyo.
He's shy when he
first meets people,
but after he gets to
know them a little,
he can open up to
them, be himself..
Because of
what he is,
Kyo can never be accepted into
the Zodiac like he wants...
But, isn't
it better
that he can be accepted
by normal people,
for who
he is?
That... is exactly what
I've always wanted.
I guess that's why I
get so angry with him.
Because he can't
even see what he has.
He's blinded by
that foolish desire
to join the
very same family
I've spent my life
trying to run away from...
Yuki, people do accept you. A
lot more than you know.
I mean...
just think of all the
girls at school who like you.
They always talk
about how nice you are...
But that
isn't me.
You say they accept
me because I'm nice?
Well, I only act nice because
I want them to accept me.
Not because it's
how I really feel...
I'm not a good person.
I'm just... selfish.
The weather didn't say
a thing about rain...
But what's a day without
surprises, I guess...
This is
bad...
Yuki! What is it...?
Where are we going?
A field?
No, just a little vegetable
garden I take care of.
Then... did
you do all this?
Uh huh. This is
my secret base.
Wow, it's even
better than I pictured!
So, you
came here
to try and protect it
from the storm, right?
I'll help if I can.
Just show me what to do!
Miss Honda, you
are a good person.
Who? Me...? You
really think so?
No one's ever told me that
before... Thank you so much!
But maybe I'm only being
nice so you'll like me!
Maybe I'm just
being selfish!
I don't think you
could if you wanted to.
I don't know
about that.
Mom said everyone can
be selfish sometimes.
But then again, she also
said it's always better
to give them the
benefit of the doubt...
No one really
starts out kind.
All we know how to
do at first is want.
We want food, we want
attention...
It's just natural
survival instinct, I guess...
But kindness
is something
that we all have
to learn as we go.
It's something that grows and
develops slowly over time...
The same way our
bodies do... And so,
kindness can come in all
sorts of shapes and sizes...
[Kyoko] True kindness isn't
something we're born with.
It's something we have to work
at. We have to mold it,
and shape it within ourselves.
Not everyone has it.
But, I think everyone
has the potential.
Sometimes you just have
to look really close
before you can
tell it's there...
Ever since Mom
told me that,
I've always tried to look
for the good in everyone.
It's hard sometimes.
But it's worth it,
because I get to see all
the different shapes
that kindness
can take...
For example, I think yours
is sort of like a candle...
Whenever
you're around,
you always seem to bring
just a little bit more light
into the room.
Everything's brighter,
and it just makes
me want to smile...
Oh, but now you're looking
at me like I'm crazy...
Ah, uh.. I'm sorry,
it's just, uh...
I guess I'm not used
to talking like this...
But I'm glad
that we are..
When you're comfortable
enough with someone
that you can share
your feelings,
I'd say that's usually
a pretty good sign
that you're getting to
be closer friends!
Oops! It got
away from me!
I guess that's a good sign
that I should stop talking
and protect
the base!
[Kyoko] It's not always easy to
see the good in people, Tohru.
In some people,
you might even doubt
that it's there at all...
But if you can somehow,
find a way to believe...
Sometimes, that's all it
takes to help someone,
to give them
the strength
to find the good
in themselves...
Hooray! We
saved the base!
Yes. But we're a little
worse for wear, aren't we.
Maybe we should pick
something while we're here.
You think?
Umm... I guess the
leeks are ready.
Ahh-hh-h leeks..
uughch...
Miss Honda...
I've been thinking.
Next time you play that
game, could I play too?
Sure! Of
course you can!
You just didn't seem too
interested before...
Well, I.. When I saw
everyone together like that,
I guess I let my
shyness get the best of me...
But next time...
I'd like to join you.
I'll keep
trying.
Maybe I can still learn
to open up more...
That's wonderful! I'll
introduce you to Hana and Uo.
They're
really great...
And I know they'll both be
excited to to meet you...
uh, I mean,
I think Uo's always
looking for another victim
to beat at Rich
Man-Poor Man!
Thanks for
the warning!
I think that's
the first time
I've ever really
seen Yuki smile...
Eat up,
everyone!
Are you crazy,
I hate leeks!
Leeks, onions, miso, am
I leaving anything out?
Hey, miso's okay as
long as it's soup...
I'm sorry, I guess
I didn't know.
I can make something
else for you if you want.
Just tell me
what you'd like!
Just eat.
It really is a
shame that
these two can't
get along better...
I have to wonder
how it would be
if Kyo knew that Yuki
admired him a little bit...
Who knows?
I'll bet there's
even something
about Yuki that
Kyo admires...
[Shigure] Umm, Yuki?
Kyo's already passed out...
If they could just
understand that,
maybe there's a chance
they'd actually stop fighting!
You know..
all this time..
I simply misunderstood
you.. I'm sorry.
No, please..
I'm sorry..
From now on, let's be
the best of friends!
On second thought,
that's a little scary!
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
[Tohru] Ah, what
a cute little girl!
[Yuki] She's had her
heart set on marrying him
since we were little kids.
For whatever that's worth.
It's pretty silly, I know.
[Tohru]
And, I think every girl
dreams about getting
married one day.
Kagura just dreams a
little louder than most.
[Kyo] You see what
happens when she's around...
It's always like that.
She's crazy.
[Tohru] When you have
someone who love's you
as much as she does, you
should really feel pretty lucky.