I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
What is that?
Sounds like
she's here early.
Oh, I didn't know you
were expecting anyone...
Ah-ah, not so fast, Kyo...
Hello?
Strange...
There's no one here...
But I distinctly remember
closing that door...
So somebody must have-
Are you Tohru Honda?
Uhhh... yes?
Oh, um... Well
that's-I mean, umm...
Yes?
I'm... Kagura...
That's my name. Kagura Sohma.
Kagura Sohma... Hi.
Ah, what a cute
little girl...
Please, I... I heard
that Kyo was here, and-
Please tell me
it's true? Is he?
Oh.. Yes, of
course. Kyo's here.
Would you like to
come in and see him?
Kyo...?
Kagura!
I don't believe it... It...
It's really you! Kyo! KYO!
I wonder...
Sohma's a pretty
common name, I guess.
So it could just be
a coincidence...
But maybe...
Maybe it means
she's one of the
Zodiac animals, too!
Kyo!
Why did you run
away for so long?
You didn't call me...
Or send a card...
Where were you?
Oh darling...
I missed you SO MUCH!
Love! You had me
worried sick!
Well, it appears
we'll be needing
another door,
doesn't it.
Sometimes it feels like
the whole world
is conspiring to
destroy my house...
I'm.. sorry...
Oh, I was just kidding...
This is normal.
It's Kagura's way of
showing affection.
I would have
never guessed...
So then... from
the looks of it,
she must really
like Kyo a lot...
Kagura does tend to get
a little carried away
with her emotions...
That's especially true
when she's around Kyo...
You might not believe it, but
she's two years older than us.
Than you... She's also
part of the zodiac.
Oh, I knew it! That's
great! Which animal is she?
I figured that would have
been obvious at this point.
[Kagura] Do you even think
about my feelings? No!
I'm sorry, I uh, I guess I've
been a little distracted.
Kyo? Darling? What happened?
You're hurt! Oh, no, no!
Speak to me! Who
did this to you?!
Um... you, I think.
It's cold in here...
Yes, I noticed that too.
I'm sorry... But, when I
saw Kyo I got so happy...
all my love just came out
at once... I couldn't help it.
It's like she's become a
totally different person...
But it is really your
fault too, Kyo...
If you'd just
remembered to call me,
you wouldn'tve made
me miss you so hard!
Who says I forgot? Maybe I
didn't want to call you!
Oh, silly, yes you did... We
are getting married, after all.
Since when?!
You mean you
don't remember?
When we were kids! You
asked me to marry you!
Only 'cause you were
gonna kill me if I didn't!
Oh, so the two of you are
engaged! That's wonderful!
At least now, he'll
have someone else
to fight
instead of me...
Congratulations.
You guys!
We really do make
the best couple,
since we're both members
of the Zodiac...
Well, Kyo's not
officially a member,
but he's still cursed,
so it's almost the same...
We can still
understand each other
in a way that no
one else can...
And that's good...
But the best thing is we can
hug each other all we want,
and we don't
transform!
I don't believe it!
Kyo didn't turn into a cat!
See! It's okay for
Zodiac members to hug!
Why is that?
It's a mystery
to us, too.
Though we've seen
it enough to know
it isn't just a
fluke with Kagura...
She's one of a
kind, granted,
but she's not the only
girl in the Zodiac...
Really? There are
more girls?
Do you think I'll get
to meet them some day?
Kyo! You have to tell me! And
be honest! Do you love me?
Do you hate me? Because
I love you! I do!
More than anything else
in the whole wide world!
Uhhh...
I'll prove it!
I'll cook for you! Everyday!
I'll do anything!
Even if you cheat on me,
I can forgive a
one-time fling!
No one else loves you this
much, do they? No! Just me!
We should always be
together, don't you think?
I just told you what you think!
Now say something, dammit!
Ahh, it pains
my heart...
But moving on- Tohru,
correct me if I'm wrong,
but aren't you something
of a cat lover yourself?
That's me! The Year
of the Cat Fan Club!
Rival.
But I'm not
going to lose!
Tohru, what do you like
best about Kyo?
Because I like
everything! Everything!
The good things,
the bad things-
I like them all!
I love Kyo no
matter what,
even if he changes
into his other fo-
Shut your mouth,
right now.
One more word,
and... and I'll...
And you'll WHAT, love?!
You should call
"mercy", Kyo...
Ah, I almost forgot
about the laundry!
Laundry?
It's too bad I didn't
get a chance to hear
which Zodiac
animal Kagura is...
Oh well, who knows... I can
ask her myself someday...
I do hope the two of
us get to be friends.
That's not Kyo's
shirt, is it?
I didn't see
you there!
So, is that
Kyo's shirt?
No, not yet. These
are Yuki's clothes.
I haven't even
started on Kyo's...
but they're
next on the list.
Don't worry,
I'll do it!
If that's okay with
you. It is, right?
I don't know...
I said I'll do it!
I really want to!
So please,
please can I?
Oh, ah... well...
Okay! If you insist.
Yaye! Thank
you so much!
Don't mention it...
Kyo! Okay, take
everything off!
Stop it!
What are you doing?!
Your laundry, silly!
Now take off your clothes!
Or do I have to wash
you along with them?!
Where are you going?
Away from you!!
Ah! Kyo!
Don't worry. I'm sure
he'll wander back
when he gets hungry.
Oh. What's the matter?
Why is Kyo so mad at me?
I don't understand.
You know... he might
not really be angry.
Sometimes he
just doesn't-
That stink! How could
you let him wear this?
My poor,
sweet darling!
You'll have clean
clothes from now on,
or I'm not the future
Mrs. Kyo Sohma!
I guess if you don't
need anything,
I'll just go hang up
Yuki's shirts now...
Let's see...
how much detergent? hmm...
Maybe a little bit more...
One more scoop, for love. Ooh!
Better yet, the whole thing!
Ah, there
you are...
Are you still going
out to shop for dinner?
Oh. Uh-huh.
I'll come
with you.
Sure.
Oh, yeah...
Perfect.
Now when Kyo comes home,
he can have a nice,
fresh cup of tea!
I'm guessing you've
noticed by now.
It would be sort
of hard not to...
But Kagura has a bit
of a one-track mind
when it
comes to Kyo.
She's had her heart
set on marrying him
since we were
little kids,
for whatever that's worth.
It's pretty silly, I know...
Oh no, not at all!
I think it's amazing.
Uh... you... do?
I mean, that kind of devotion
is pretty rare, you know?
To like someone so
much for that long...
It's really
wonderful, isn't it?
I hadn't thought
of it like that.
In fact... I think
she'd be a great person
to have as a friend.
You should try. I think you'd
be a good influence on her.
I don't know about that...
But it's nice of you to say...
"Kyo! Q! I love you!"-
Waah-ha!! No more smell!
I'm a perfect wife!
Finally... Now I just
gotta get my shirt back,
then I get the
hell outta here...
Maybe I should wring it out a
little to make it dry faster!
Dry! Damn... you!!
Uh...
Tell me you didn't do
what I just think you did!
My love...
My shirt!
And I really liked
this one, too...
I'm sorry, darling...
I promise, I'll
fix it right away...
Here, you can wear
this one 'til then.
It's soaking wet!
But, that's because
I washed it for you.
Is there anything of
mine you didn't wash!
Your pants...
What am I supposed to do now?!
Go around half-naked?!
You want me to get
pneumonia, is that it?!
Kagura... how much
detergent did you use?
All of it!
Is something burning?
Oh no, the tea!
Coming through.
Don't we look lovely.
I can't believe
you're laughing.
Oh, right...
'Now I'm mad'.
I... I'm sorry...
I didn't do it on purpose...
I know that, Kagura.
You still did it!
I'm sorry... I really am...
Please, Kyo... I'm sorry..
Yeah, so what "sorry" isn't
going to get us a new kitchen.
What do you want
me to do?!
Oooh! That hurts!
Well, you see...
It- It's a long story...
That's all right. I think
I can guess what happened.
Uhh... I'll help
you clean up.
I can do it.
But it's too much work
for you all by yourself.
No, please! Let me
do it! I want to...
It's my fault the
kitchen's like this...
At least she's
being consistent.
She wouldn't let
me help, either.
Please, it's okay...
I'll do it all.
Well... if you insist...
Do you really think it's
okay to leave her in there?
Don't worry. Kagura's
always been the resilient type.
I'm sure she just needs
some time to herself.
Of course, the real
crisis here,
is that we won't be
able to cook any dinner
while the
kitchen's wrecked...
I guess we're just going
to have grit our teeth
and call
for take-out.
and I was so looking
forward to another
of Tohru's delicious
home-cooked meals.
So... where'd the
other home-wrecker go?
He's still busy
sulking, I think.
We'd probably do well to keep
our distance for a while...
I'm gonna burst...
Ahhh, full, full, full...
You, Miss Honda?
I couldn't eat
another bite.
Oh... but what about
Kagura and Kyo?
We shouldn't let their
dinners get cold.
Ah... so let's see...
Am I brave enough to go
look for Kyo just yet?
Mmm. No. But I think I
can chance the kitchen...
Kagura, you know we
ordered you some dinner...
I'm pretty sure it'll
taste better while it's hot.
Thanks, but...
I'll eat later...
You can just leave it
out there for now.
How's Kyo?
Is he still angry?
Your guess is as
good as mine.
He still hasn't come
down from hiding.
You're angry at me
too, aren't you.
No, I wouldn't say
that. I'm not angry.
Of course... I can't
say I'd want to...
repeat this
little incident.
Shigure, please let
me stay here, too...
I don't think I can
leave knowing Kyo's
living in this house
with another woman.
Woman-? We're talking
about Tohru now, right?
No, I can't wait
that long!
I have to force Kyo to make
up his mind, tonight!
That's not a
good idea.
You don't know!
You don't understand how a
woman feels when she's in love!
Yes I do.
At least, I've felt enough
women to venture a guess.
Sorry. That's your cue to
say, "Shigure, you perv!"
And roll your eyes,
slap me, whatever.
Shigure! You... big... perv!
Ha ha ha ha! Pervert!
Pervert! Ha ha ha ha!
Everything's so clean...
Kagura and Kyo still
haven't eaten their dinners.
They must be starving.
Kagura...?
This'll take all
night. I know it.
Has she been working
this whole time?
I'm so hungry...
Hi there.
Um... I made you a snack.
I noticed you hadn't
eaten your dinner yet,
and I thought you
might be hungry...
So I made some rice
balls with the leftovers...
I hope it's okay that
I served them cold...
I can heat them
up if you want!
Eh... no... I like
them this way.
Okay then... Now
why don't we see
if we can't finish
fixing this door?
I thought it might make the job
more fun if we worked together.
Yes... That
would be nice...
Good!
Before we start...?
Yes?
Can I please have
one more riceball?
Sure!
Hey, lookie, lookie!
It's a cat, right?
It's so cute!
Uh-huh...
Look... I made one, too.
A little rat!
You can tell?
Sure I can!
It's adorable!
Why thank you very much! I'll
put it up... right... here.
I'm gonna do
another one!
All right.
I will too!
Tohru, what are
you gonna make?
Let's see...
How about a dog?
Okay! Then I'll
make... another cat!
Ooh! And this time
I'll make the tail...
--Tohru?
--Yes?
Thank you... I hope we can
be friends from now on?
Yes... I'd like that.
Kyo...
You're not really planning
on staying up here
the whole
night, are you?
Better believe it.
Kagura's still down there!
You don't want
her to be here?
What do you think? You see
what happens when she's around.
It's always like
that. She's crazy!
And she won't
ever shut up
about all that stupid
"marriage" crap...
I can't stand it.
I think it's sweet.
When you have someone
who loves you
as much as
she does...
You should really feel
pretty lucky... You know?
And, I think every girl dreams
about getting married one day...
Kagura just dreams a
little... louder than most.
Here you go!
Kyo, you have a dream too,
don't you? To beat Yuki?
Isn't that why you were
up in the mountains
for so long?
Training?
Hm? Yeah- Oh.
Guess Shigure told you...
That must have
been really hard...
Being out there
all by yourself...
No. I wasn't alone.
I was with my master.
Oh. A master! He must
be really strong then.
Are you kidding?
He could flatten that sissy
rat-boy with one punch!
My master's as strong as
they come! He's a Sohma.
But he never treated
me like the others do.
He's been teaching
me how to fight
ever since I was
a little kid!
Sure, he put me through hell
up there in the mountains,
but those were some of
the best days of my life!
It's like every day was
an adventure, you know?
I'd wake up every
morning and ask myself,
"What's he
gonna teach me?"
"How much stronger am
I gonna get today?"
It was great!
Ahh... listen to me!
Just talking about
it gets me pumped up!
But this must seem
pretty stupid
to someone
like you, huh.
Oh! No! It's
fascinating!
I guess I just
don't really know
anything about
fighting, is all...
Not to say that I'm not
interested to learn!
And I mean, I do
know a little bit!
I have a couple moves
I can show you!
Um, let's see...
Right Straight!
You suck.
I think I've discovered
something else new about Kyo...
Underneath that angry
face he usually makes,
he's been hiding this
little awkward smile...
Kyo! Darling!
Goodbye my love! Take care
of yourself 'til I come back!
Glad to see everything's
back to normal.
Incidentally, did
you ever figure out
which animal
Kagura is?
No, not yet.
Kyo, be nice, or I'm not
gonna kiss you goodbye!
Who needs it?!
That's it! Kyo, you jerk!
I'm leaving you, Love!
Hello! It is I!
Your ever-reliable
local paperboy,
come to deliver the
news of the day!
This is bad.
Ah, thanks for
your hard work.
Oh sure... It's my job.
Sorry I was a little
late this morning. Bye!
Hey, I figured out Kagura's
zodiac animal! She's a boar!
Um... That's
cheating, I think.
Kagura... You know, I think I'm
beginning to understand better
why it is you like
Kyo so much...
He really does have a
lot of good qualities...
And the more I
learn about them,
the more I want see
him the way you do.
Kyo! You two-timer!
I thought she was going to
forgive his little flings...
I will forgive him!
Right after I kill him!
What the hell
did I do?!
'Scuse me... Maybe I
should start over...
What I'm
trying to say is,
I hope I can
be like you
when it comes to finding
all of the good qualities
in the people that
I care about...
They're not always
easy to see...
You want to...
be like me?
Uh, huh. It's
wonderful the way you find
so many things to
like about one person...
I don't know
what to say...
Put on some
clothes!
Okay, bye, bye!
Oh, and I'll bring
you a new shirt
next time I come
over, Kyo! Love you!
Hmph.
Goodbye! See you
again soon!
Hey! What's that
look for?
Nothing... You're
just so... lucky.
Don't you even start!
C'mon! We're gonna be late!
Oh, well... there was
such a commotinon,
that I couldn't even
do any gardening.
Ah, the base! Those leeks
we picked were delicious.
Are you planting
something new?
Yes, strawberries.
Really? I can't wait!
I love strawberries!
I thought you might...
That's why I'm planting them.
Oh... Thanks...
Kyo! Stop right there!
I almost forgot to give you
your goodbye kiss!
C'mon, pucker up!
Kiss me! Kiss, kiss...
All of a sudden,
I'm feeling like there are a
few things I need to do...
I'd like to learn more about
Kyo and Yuki if I can...
About the things
they like...
and the things
they don't like...
I think that might
help me to understand
them both a
little bit better.
And who knows?
Maybe it will
help me to find
all the good qualities in them
that I haven't seen before!
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
[Shigure] Ah, I see...
And if memory serves,
you were planning to
move back into the house
once the
work was done.
Is that right?
[Tohru] I really had
it wrong this time.
I don't know why I thought
I'd be able to go on
living here
with everyone,
like a family.
[Kagura] Tohru you get
to be the riceball!
[Tohru] A riceball doesn't
belong in a Fruits Basket.
Well as far as goodbyes go,
that felt pretty good, I guess.
Except, I didn't think
leaving Yuki and the others
would make me
feel so lonely.
The truth of it is, I didn't
want to leave them at all.