I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
[Tohru]
So, it's almost May.
Some of these should be
ready to pick soon, right?
[Yuki] Uh-huh...
I'd say, the carrots,
the turnips...
the leeks.
Oh, and the
strawberries.
Oh! The strawberries are
almost ready? I can't wait!
Yes... they should
be delicious.
Are you okay?
I'm fine... I guess it's
just a little chillier
out here than
I expected.
In that case...
We're almost done here...
Why don't you go on
back to the house?
Oh... are
you sure...?
Well, I'm
hungry, too...
Okay, when you
put it like that--!
I'll go back and make
us something to eat.
[Tohru] It's only
been a few days
since our unexpected meeting
with Akito at school...
But, already, Yuki seems to be
in a much more cheerful mood...
I'm so glad...
Now then... What
should I make for...
lunch?
Could this be someone...
from the Zodiac?!
Miss Honda!
Th-there's...
What?!
There's something
under my clothes!
Ah, dammit,
I'm hungry!
Tohru should be back soon...
Try being patient for once.
Forget it! I'll just
make something myself.
Hold on, Kyo... I
have a better idea.
You can snack on
these to tie you over
until Tohru
gets home...
Are you crazy?! You know
damn well I hate miso!
You know...
You really shouldn't
waste food like
that... Terrible...
There, you see?
Here they are... now...
You want lunch? Here.
Skin this and eat it.
Uh... is that Aya?
It is! But... what
is he doing here?
Never mind! Just skin
this thing and eat it!
Hold on... I think you
need to calm down, Yuki...
[Shigure] That
was Ayame Sohma.
And as I'm sure you
noticed, he's the snake.
[Tohru]
Ayame... oh!
We'll let him
sleep for a while.
Snakes naturally
hibernate in the winter...
I imagine that's part
of the reason Aya
has always been
sensitive to the cold.
If he's
not careful,
it can cause him to
transform like this...
Aya, Hatori, and I
grew up together.
We were in the same class
through grade school,
middle school,
and high school!
We were inseparable.
So much so,
people called us the
"Three Musketeers".
Oh! Wow! Did
they really?!
More like the "Three
Idiots" if you ask me.
How did Hatori put up
with you for so long?
So... What did Aya do to
upset you so much, Yuki?
I won't even say it,
it's so disgusting...
[Aya] Come now,
it wasn't so bad!
You could show a
little more forgiveness
to your own
brother...
Eh?
Did...
he say 'brother'?
Allow me to explain
what happened.
I was on my way here,
when a sudden chill in the
air caused me to transform.
In my search for heat, I sensed
a warm body drawing near,
and I naturally
clung to it!
I suppose you could
say it was- instinct.
Greetings,
everyone!
And how have you
been... little brother?
He's like a
grown-up Yuki!
If we all followed
our instincts...
I would have snapped you in
two when I had the chance!
What's the big deal? What
exactly did he do to you?
Oh! Well, you
see, he uh...
Oh... Lucky Kyo. I'd heard
you were staying here.
I told you before!
Stop calling me that!
Lucky Kyo. You
haven't changed.
I said stop!
It been too
long, Shigure...
Yes, since
New Years'.
What a shame.
You haven't
forgotten about me
while we were been
apart... have you?
Not a day has gone by that you
haven't been on my mind... Aya.
Yes!
No, no, no!
[Tohru] Um... I'm starting
to get the feeling
Ayame's personality is very
different from Yuki's...
By the way, this is the
one and only Tohru Honda!
You came to see
her today, right?
Oh, yes
that's right!
I'm sorry
about earlier...
I am Yuki's older
brother... Ayame...
Oh, right! Pleased
to meet you!
So, you really
do exist...
The princess I've...
heard so much about.
A single
blooming flower
trapped in a house
of stinking men!
Are they treating
you well, princess?
You make it sound like
she's been kidnapped...
Brother... You're being
rude. Stop making fun of her.
Making fun?
Honestly. I mean Tohru nothing
but the highest respect!
So, princess, why don't
you bring us some tea?
And lunch
would be nice.
That's not
respect!
Of course,
you're right...
What was I thinking?
Let me try again.
Come Tohru...
...We're going
out to eat!
Uh... but... I
don't know...!
Don't worry!
It's my treat!
Now, there's no use
getting angry at me...
Very good. Feel free to
order anything you like.
Although, I'd highly recommend
the potsticker plate.
Don't worry about Yuki and the
others... They're big boys.
I do think they can manage
something on their own...
But, still I--I'm not
sure I should've come...
Well, I hope you
won't deny me
the pleasure of treating
you to lunch...
Oh, no! I'm sorry! I didn't
mean to sound ungrateful!
Good. Then it's settled...
Waiter! Two potsticker plates!
Coming right up!
I'm just being
swept away!
I have to
tell you...
It's been one surprise after
another, meeting you today...
Yuki's never
mentioned you before,
let alone that you're
part of the zodiac...
I suppose that shouldn't
come as news to me...
As you know, Yuki and I don't
get along very well. Or rather,
I should say we've never
really been very close...
You see, we're
ten years apart...
And when Yuki was born...
he got sick fairly easily,
so he was kept separated,
much of the time...
Separated?
I, on the other hand, grew
up doing whatever I liked.
Because of our
separation,
I was only vaguely aware
that I even had a brother...
By the time I realized it, a
deep gap had formed between us,
that we have never
been able to bridge.
That is our story.
I was told... Yuki saw Akito
at school the other day...
You met him
too, I think?
How do I
put this...?
I've never had much
interaction with him myself...
but for Yuki, Akito is
a source of great fear...
Even now, at his age, I'm not
sure that fear has subsided...
And so... while I did
want to meet you today,
more than
that...
I wanted to make sure
Yuki was all right...
I'm glad to see he's
doing well, but...
I was hoping I'd have a chance
to play the big brother.
Do you still
hope that?
Maybe he's trying
to close the gap...
It's odd in a way...
The more the years go by,
the more I come to
understand things
I didn't understand
when I was a child...
I think, "When that happened,
I should have done this,"
or "When that happened,
I should have said this..."
That sort
of thing...
Only now have I begun
to realize all the ways
I could have been a
better brother then...
And I confess, I feel a
certain amount of regret
that things are the
way they are...
I wish I could
go back,
and correct the mistakes
I made as a child.
But I suppose every adult
wishes that to some degree.
You know, my Mom...
My Mom told me one time...
When she first became a parent,
she finally understood
how it felt to be an adult.
But still...
As important as that was,
she said she never
wanted to forget...
She always wanted
to remember...
how it felt
to be a child.
Like, the first time you turned
a flip on the monkey bars,
or the first time
something upset you...
She said, if you can
remember those feelings,
then when you become an adult
and have children of your own,
you'll be able to understand
each other much better.
And even when you don't agree,
you can still meet half-way...
Besides... It's just more fun
to think that way, you know?
I'm sorry! I'm supposed to
be talking about you and Yuki!
I guess I got a little
sidetracked there.
Oh, I know I
had a point--
Maybe you and Yuki can try
to meet each other half-way!
Okay, here
you go!
[Tohru] I guess that
doesn't make any sense...
[Aya]
No, it does...
Some people say the
greatest things, don't they?
Uh-huh! Mom was the
best in the universe!
Um... Actually, I was talking
about you... but either way...
I think... I
understand now...
Why it is my brother's
doing so well lately...
Listen... As far
as Yuki goes...
I promise I'll keep
trying... And you...
I hope you'll continue to be
there for him when I can't...
What's this? The look
on Ayame's face...
Oh, Miss Honda!
You okay?
Uh-huh... Did everyone
get something to eat?
Never mind about that. Did my
brother give you any trouble?
Oh, no! Not at all! He
bought me a potsticker plate!
Um...
Yuki?
I was wondering... Well, do you
really not like your brother?
I mean, I know it's not
really any of my business...
I was just
curious...
I wouldn't say
I... dislike him...
He's just a little too
much for me sometimes...
Well, if that's all,
we can overcome it!
I will do all in my power
to meet you half-way...!
...my brother!
Uh... you see... it got
really cold on the way
home from
the restaurant,
and he
transformed!
And he said that if snakes
get too cold, they can die!
Well I am
a snake.
You may be a snake, but
you're no brother of mine!
You can't change
the truth, Yuki!
[Shigure] Ah, welcome
back, you two.
[Tohru] But Yuki, if
you could have seen
the look on his face
at the restaurant...
you'd know that Ayame
truly cares about you.
Shigure... Have you
picked out a place
for me to
sleep tonight?
Oh? You're
staying over?
Hush. I'm
still sleeping.
Get off
of me!
I'm sorry, but I
had no other choice.
Yuki locked the
door to his room,
so I couldn't
sleep in there.
Why the hell didn't you
go to Shigure's room?
Like yesterday?!
Because... if I had... Shigure
would've kept me up all night.
Aya... not in front of
the children, please.
Oh, cut
it out!
Just ignore them...
ignore them...
Don't worry... If it
bothers you that much,
tonight I'll sleep
in Tohru's room.
You will not!
[Tohru] It's the morning
of the third day
since Ayame
came to visit...
But, unfortunately,
it seems like the gap
between him and Yuki
has only grown wider...
Really! Aya's there? I haven't
seen him since New Year's!
[Tohru] For three
days now...
[Momiji] Maybe
I'll go visit him!
Oh... Then again,
he probably just wants to
spend some time with Yuki.
Which reminds
me... How is Yuki?
Uh...
well...
Yuki...
What...
Is he sick?
Well...
not exactly.
Don't worry.
I get it...
Yeah... Uh-huh...
Figures...
Hey, Haru... Is it weird
for Aya to leave his shop?
I mean, he is
the owner...
Oh? So you mean Ayame
runs his own business?
That's right...
He sells outfits
for nurses, stewardesses,
maids, things
like that...
So then, he
makes... uniforms?
Well, uh...
not exactly.
Aya says he makes
fantasies come true!
My, my! This
is unexpected!
Dammit...
He's here...
Welcome back!
But how nice! You boys
wanted to see me so badly
you came straight
home from school...
And here
I thought
Tohru and I
would have the whole
afternoon to ourselves!
That's what we
were afraid of!
What is that you
were looking at?
Oh, just some old albums of us
in our high-school days... See?
There's
Hatori, too...
I don't believe it! Shigure
and Hatori both look so young!
And Ayame-- he looked
exactly like Yuki does now!
Pretty cute,
weren't we?
[Tohru] Uh-huh! So Ayame,
you wore your hair long,
even when you were
in high-school?
That's right... Of course,
I had to bend a few rules...
Here, Yuki... You
come look, too...
Now's your chance
to learn something
new about
your brother!
I'll pass,
thank you.
Then, you leave
me no choice...
I'll simply have to tell
you the whole story
of how I got to keep my
long hair at school...
What for?!
See... it was the very start of
my first year in high school,
You like hearin'
yourself talk, dontcha?
I allowed
the color,
but I didn't allow you
to wear your hair long.
Have it cut
by tomorrow.
I'm sorry, sir... but...
I come from a royal family.
I've kept it
secret until now,
but soon I must return
to my own country.
And it is our age-old
custom that members
of the royal family should
always wear their hair long,
in honor of the
high king Rurubara,
who, it is said, during the
fourth year of his reign,
was visited by a divine
image -It was Kandra,
shimmering with heavenly
light of red and gold!
Kandra began to chant,
"Ma Rudu Muni!"
And a blue light burst
forth from his forehead.
At this moment, Rurubara's
true spirit was set free!
And just as the vast springs
of strength and wisdom
were swelling
within him,
so too did his hair begin to
sprout forth from his head!
At this same moment,
the prince Kasipaloo,
who had been sleeping
securely in his bed,
let out a
mighty cry.
"Kanpanil!"
he shouted,
Uh, excuse me,
I just remembered,
I'm very late for
an important meeting.
I have
to go.
But I still have more
to tell you about Kandra.
No! It's fine!
Your hair is fine!
And that's how I convinced him
to let me wear my hair long.
Y- you're a member
of a royal family!?
Duh, he was
lying! Come on!
Those were
the days...
Idiots...
And here's something else
I bet you didn't know:
Aya... was Student
Council President!
Was he
really?!
Stop fooling
around. Let's go.
He was a natural
choice, I suppose.
What with the way he looked
and the way he acted,
he was really very popular
with the other boys.
And under
his term,
many of the old school
rules were... relaxed.
You certainly had
a way about you...
I don't know...
I always thought
Ha'ri would have made
a much better
president than me.
Do you
remember?
The time we all went on
that class field trip?
Of course! How
could I forget?
So... what
happened?
I don't
believe it!
It sounds like Yuki's actually
taking an interest! Ayame!
This is your chance!
This is your chance to
finally bridge the gap!
Yes... well,
you see...
there was a group of
students during this trip...
who, we'll say... wandered
into the 'red-light district.
Please, reserve your judgment
until I've explained.
Although it would
have been difficult
for any healthy young man
to resist this place,
we weren't actually
the ones who went.
Of course, it's not like
we hadn't seen it before.
Idiot...
I can't believe he just
said that out loud.
As it
happened...
One of
the teachers
found out where they'd
gone... And then...!
It was decided that
all of the boys
were to be expelled
from school.
Naturally, as Student Council
President, I objected!
A meeting was called between
the students, their parents,
the principal, and the
teachers involved...
For a group of minors to set
foot in a red-light district--
this is by no means
an act to be praised.
Laws are put in
place to be obeyed...
Otherwise...
we lose order.
And with that
being said...
I must also express my
concern over what I see
as a condemnation of our
natural human instincts!
I submit that the desires
which led these boys astray
were fueled by perhaps the
most noble of human instincts-
the instinct to
procreate the species!
Should we damn them for
feeling these natural urges?
President...
Ayame. You're being
unusually serious today.
Yes. Quite a departure
from your normal antics.
At this time, I would like
to offer you a proposal!
Let us offer a hand of rescue
to these wayward youths.
Let us help them
to understand
their sometimes confusing
natural desires...
From now on...!
They may direct their
desire toward me!
As a chosen representative
of this student body,
it is only fitting
that this heavy burden
should fall on
my shoulders.
And furthermore... Since
we will all be boys,
parents and teachers will
have nothing to fear!
So send me
your desire!
In the service of
my fellow students,
I am prepared
to receive!
He's gone mad!
Insane!
Get him
out of here!
Don't worry. Despite how it
looks, I know what I'm doing.
Thus concludes my
wonderful story!
You mean
stupid!
Excuse me! But
because of that,
everyone avoided
being expelled.
How so?
Well, after that,
Hatori stepped in
and said a
few words...
But Aya was our president
until the very end!
You're
kidding!
What do you
think Yuki?
Has this helped you understand
your older brother?
I think you
should leave.
Oh no! The gap!
Well, I'll have
to do better...
Let me tell you about the time
I kidnapped the school mascot!
No, I really think
you should leave.
It all started one
spring morning...
Shigure! Get
rid of him!
But why?
This is fun!
Yes,
it's fun!
You're killin'
me here!
Even so, I really don't
think he'll listen to me...
The only person he
does listen to is--
Hey.
The door was unlocked,
so I let myself in.
Oh! Hi
Hatori!
Speak of
the devil!
Ha'ri! To what do
we owe the pleasure?
Hatsuharu... He said I
should come take you home.
So, what do you say you wrap
things up here... And we'll go.
Well then,
bye-bye.
I guess with all
the commotion,
you and I didn't
get to talk much.
Weren't you the one
causing the commotion?
You'll see me again,
little brother.
All right, Ha'ri.
Ready when you are...
Until next
time, Shigure!
Mmm! Now it's my
turn to visit you!
Farewell,
everyone!
So, are
we walking?
[Hari] I brought
the car.
[Aya] Good!
Can I drive?
[Hari] No.
What... was
that all about?
[Shigure] As long
as I remember,
Ha'ri's been the only one who
can tell Aya what to do...
Aya really
admires him...
He sees a lot of good
qualities in Hatori
that he's always
wished he had himself.
But since he
doesn't...
He figures staying close to
Ha'ri is the next best thing.
He actually told
me that once.
And with a straight
face, no less.
Anyway, letting Ha'ri
boss him around
is just one way Aya
shows his admiration.
I'm sorry about this-- putting
you to all this trouble.
If that's the
way you feel,
maybe you should
think before you act.
I did think.
I thought I'd be
able to get Yuki
to open up to me
a little bit...
I wouldn't let it
bother you just yet.
Yuki is still
very young...
Give him some time to figure
things out on his own.
There's no
need to rush.
You know, in a way...
Tohru reminded me of you.
She's very good
about considering
other people's
feelings.
At least, she's much
better at it than I am.
And like you...
...she has a way of telling me
exactly what I need to hear.
I really liked listening
to Ayame's stories...
That man needs
some serious help.
The gap!
Um, I don't know, I
mean, I thought he was--
Although...
The way he's not afraid
to show his admiration...
You know, when he sees
qualities he'd like to have
in other people...
That's... That's good.
[Mrs. Honda] You might
not always agree,
but you can always
meet half-way.
[Yuki] Haru...
Listen... I... I
just want to say
thank you for
worrying about me.
[Mrs. Honda] Besides...
It's just more fun
to think that
way, you know?
Oh, you
know what?
I never did find out
what kind of shop it is
that sells outfits
for nurses and maids!
What're you
talkin' about?
She means a
lingerie store.
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
What is it? Spending some
time with your friends?
Yeah, it's the first
anniversary of Mom's death,
so we're going
to her grave.
Would it be alright
if I came along?
Hey, if your going to the
grave then I'm going to!
Why are you
telling me?
What are
you drawing!?
I really have found a
wonderful home here.
Living in this house
together with all of them.
And I'm so greatful for
every day I've had here.
So Mom, I just
want you to know...
that while your up
there watching over me
you don't have
to worry anymore...
I'm home.