I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
Call a doctor! Or a vet!
Or anybody!
Mr. Postman! It's terrible!
You see?! They're animals!
Well, uh... Yes, they certainly
are... Here's your mail!
No, no! We've got
to do something!!
I wish my dog was
this smart. Good day!
Dammit! How am I supposed
to come up with an excuse
if both of you transform too?!
Don't you dare try to blame
this on us, you stupid cat!
Go ahead... Say that again!
Stupid Cat.
Why you little--
Cut it out! Both of you!
You mean... they talk too?!
Anyway, it's too
late for excuses...
We might as well
tell her the truth...
Tohru? I'm a dog.
Yuki here, he's a rat.
That's Kyo.
Don't let his temper scare you.
He's got a bit of
a chip on his shoulder.
So this is... normal?
Strange choice
of words, but yes.
Our family has lived with
this curse for generations.
We transform into the twelve
animals of the Chinese Zodiac.
Sorry. The twelve
animals, plus the cat.
Anyway...
whenever our bodies come
under a great deal of stress,
or when we're hugged
by a member of the
opposite sex, we transform.
After a little while, we change
back. The only thing is, uh...
...we're naked.
Well... we must seem
pretty strange to
you at this point, huh?
Yeah... but... it's not your
fault if your family's cursed...
A family curse... I guess that
would explain a few things...
If Yuki turns into an animal
whenever a girl hugs him,
that must be why he pushed that
fan club girl in the hall...
He didn't want her
to find out his secret!
Tohru, didn't you say you used
to wish you could be a cat?
Yeah. Uh-huh.
What's it like
seeing the real thing?
Right! It's the cat from
the Chinese Zodiac!
Like in the story!
Yes, it's hard to believe...
I know!
And I agree, the phrase
"cat-like reflexes"
doesn't really apply to him,
the way he let you
fall on him like that...
But he is a cat,
albeit clumsier than most.
Surprising really,
considering the amount of
martial arts training he's had.
I'm sure he'd tell you the same
thing himself, if he wasn't so
busy brooding like a child...
Will you shut up!
I told you it's not my fault!
If you wanna blame
somebody, blame her!
She shouldn't even be here!
Leave her out of this...
Who we choose
to allow into this house
is really none of your concern.
You're the one who
doesn't belong here.
Punk!!
Oh, Tohru, you're bleeding.
I knew Kyo was reckless with his
temper, but to act like this...?
You're still as stupid as ever.
And I'm going
to prove it to you
by giving you
exactly what you want.
Only this time...
I won't hold back.
Okay... sissy boy!
No, Yuki!
Don't worry... This goes back
a lot farther than just today...
Those two do nothing but fight
whenever they see each other.
But... uhh...
shouldn't we stop them?
No. It's okay...
It'll all be over in a second.
I told you
I wouldn't hold back...
You should've listened...
He... sent him flying...
Yuki, try not to destroy
the house, okay?
I really didn't mean
to put him in the yard...
He should learn
to keep his guard up.
Miss Honda... your hurt?
Oh! It's fine! Really! I'm okay!
But I, uh... I'm not
so sure about him...
No. The only thing
he's bruised is his ego.
I'm guessing your
dreams of being a cat
are pretty much
shattered at this point.
Well, I don't know. I wouldn't--
...say that.
It's hard to believe, Mom.
All the girls call
Yuki a "prince",
but I didn't think he could
really be so... so noble.
I just thought it was
because he was cute
and good at sports. But this...
I've never seen him
act like this at school...
...School!
Oh no! I'm late! I'm late!
I'm late! I'm late! Sorry!
I'm not so sure you want
to go in that uniform...
Ah! Suddenly she remembers
her adventures in the woods...
I don't know... It's not that
bad. Maybe no one will notice!
Uh, I think they will.
You're right... But I promised
Mom. I have to go to school!
Fine. Don't let me stop you.
A promise is a promise.
Which reminds me,
I will have to tell Akito
about everything that's
happened this morning.
You have to tell who?
Oh, sorry.
He's the head of the family.
So, then I guess...
this... Akito...
He must be someone
really important, huh?
Well, he is to us at least...
And after all, we did
just give away the big
"Sohma Family Secret."
Oh, right... That does make
sense... but I really am late.
Goodbye!
Be safe!
Since when have
you been so talkative
about our family matters?
You're planning on erasing Miss
Honda's memories, aren't you...
Just like in the old days.
That's not my intention...
This isn't like before.
Too many people knew
about us back then.
It couldn't be helped.
Fine... I'm going to school...
Thanks again for letting
me use the washing machine!
Believe me,
I did us all a favor...
Now, how did you
say you got so dirty?
L-O-V-E! We love... Yuki!
Yuki! Yuki!
So Miss Tohru,
how come the dirty clothes?
Did Prince Yuki
give you the ditch?
Good grief, those
girls give me a headache...
Their "prince" doesn't show so
they have to bother someone...
But why you, I wonder?
I can't imagine what they'd do
if they knew I was
staying at Yuki's house.
I think even Uo and Hana would
be upset if they knew...
Oh well. Silly, silly!
I better go change now.
Hello, Miss Honda.
Oh, Yuki. Hi.
So, did you tell them? Your
friends... About this morning?
Umm... I told them I tripped...
Oh! Your secret!
No! No, I didn't!
I promise I won't tell a soul!
Mom always said
it's not right to gossip!
Oh, but you don't
know me that well yet!
--No, really-
--I swear!
I'll write it in
blood if you want!
Cross my heart
and hope to die!
Whatever it takes
for you to believe me!
I'll swallow a thousand--
That's not what I meant!
I'm sorry.
I do believe you when you
say you'll keep our secret...
But it doesn't matter.
We still might have
to erase your memory.
It won't harm you.
It's something like hypnotism.
You'll simply forget everything
you saw this morning...
I know this, because this
isn't the first time
someone has learned about us...
It happened when
I was seven years old.
I was playing with
some other children
in the garden
behind our house...
After that, we had to erase
every one of those
children's memories...
Akito, am I really that strange?
Am I so strange that we
have to hide it from everyone?
Hmph... Yes.
You are that strange.
A human who turns into a rat?
What do you think they would
do you if they knew? Really?
You're a freak. They
wouldn't come near you...
They'd hate you.
Yuki?
Are you all right?
But I... I can't go
against Akito's decision,
whatever it is...
I can't stop him, no matter
how much I might want to...
That's why... I'm sorry!
Wait!!
I am so sorry! Really,
I didn't do it on purpose!
Ohh, I'm such an idiot!
I wasn't even thinking!
It's all right. Just as
long as no one else saw...
Oh... okay.
What I wanted to say was,
thank you for being
concerned about me.
But, really... It's okay.
I'm fine. I'm not scared.
So don't worry.
I mean, I completely understand
if you and your family
don't want anyone to
know about your secret.
That's why it's
called a secret, right?
So whatever you
decide is fine with me.
I want you to do what makes
you feel the most comfortable...
I don't really like the
idea of losing my memory.
And I don't want
to forget meeting Yuki...
But he's done so much for me
without asking
anything in return...
So, I guess, if
that's what I have to do...
You can erase my memory.
But afterwards, promise
you'll still be my friend?
Sorry, the amount of time before
we change back varies a bit...
It's... okay...
Yuki... where did
you learn to tie a tie?
I guess I've never been very
good at this sort of thing...
Don't feel bad.
Nobody's perfect!
Good thing you have me here.
You're a freak.
They wouldn't come near you...
They'd hate you.
Miss Honda... I-It really
didn't bother you to see?
Oh! Don't worry,
I closed my eyes in time!
No, I didn't mean that...
So... can I...
walk you to class?
Uh, huh!
But afterwards, promise
you'll still be my friend?
Thank you.
No problem.
Fixing ties is my specialty!
Uh, heh, heh, heh...
I believe...
I will trust Miss Honda...
For Yuki... and for Kyo...
even for myself...
this may be a
great opportunity...
I'm back!
Hello! We're home from school!
Shigure?
He must have gone out.
I'm going to go
put away my bag.
Okay.
Uh... what...
Don't freak out.
It's only temporary.
You can call someone
to fix it better later.
This'll at least keep
the rain out 'til then.
Yes, thank you...
I did hope I'd get to talk
to him again after he ran off...
but I don't think he
likes me very much...
Hey!
Ah! I'm here!
I'm not very good at
controlling my temper.
When I get angry,
I... I don't know.
Maybe I don't have
enough training...
I just... I can't stand
losing to that damn Yuki!
So, about this morning...
It wasn't... What I mean is...
I'm so--
I'm home! Yuki! Tohru!
Are you here? And Kyo!
I hope you're not
doing something stupid
and tearing up my house again!
Oh, forget it!
Ahh... wait! Please, don't go.
He'll be back... It's not
like he has anywhere else to go.
But never mind him. Can you
come in here for a second?
Okay...
I had a little talk
with Akito today...
He's decided that as long
as you can keep our secret,
you can stay here.
Good! So then there's...
no punishment?
Punishment? Why would we--
You can keep the secret?
Yes!
That's great news!
I won't have to lose my memory!
Shigure...
It all seems too easy,
doesn't it?
I can't help but think
Akito has something
else in store for us...
I don't know...
But don't worry so much!
Everything's going
well, enjoy it!
For now, let's just trust
Akito to do what's best...
Excuse me...
Uh... I'm sorry
to interrupt. It's just...
You've been so nice to me...
I hope it's no trouble.
Uh... No...
No, of course it isn't...
Make yourself at home, okay?
Okay!
It looks like it's going
to be okay, Mom.
Even after everything
that happened this morning,
the Sohmas have still invited
me to stay in their house!
I guess this will be
our home for a while!
Well, it not going
to clean itself!
I'll help you...
Just tell me what to do.
You'd better not...
The closest thing Yuki's
ever seen to a mop
is that haircut of his...
I think he'd just
get in the way.
That's all right.
I'll take care of it!
We all made a deal that
I'd do the housework
in exchange for my room...
I wouldn't be earning my
keep if I let you two help me!
Well I can see
we're in good hands...
I'm going to go find Kyo,
and I'll be out with
him for a while...
We should be back by lunchtime.
Sure, just leave it to me!
In that case,
I guess I'll go out too...
Fine! I'll be done
when you get back!
What was I thinking? I don't
even know where to start...
But Tohru Honda never gives up!
And that's that!
Amazing! If I
didn't know better,
I'd think I walked into
the wrong house...
Since when did we
have a rice cooker?
I found it in the trash!
Oh... by the way...
I hope you've got your appetite,
'cause lunch is almost ready!
Mmm, it's delicious.
You think so?
You don't think it's to bland?
It's perfect!
The best lunch I've ever had!
Don't be silly...
That reminds me,
I wonder where Shigure
and that stupid cat ran off to?
I don't know. He said
they'd be back by lunchtime...
Well shame on them...
It's rude to let a meal
this good get cold.
It's so strange.
I guess I still haven't
gotten used to the
idea of living here.
But here I am,
having lunch with Yuki!
Oh yeah... You went out
for a while too, didn't you?
Where'd you go? Shopping?
Oh, no... I just went out
back to my secret base.
What?
You have a secret base?!
You mean like a fort?
Or an underground hideout?!
That sounds so exciting!
I don't think it's
quite as elaborate
as what you're thinking...
But I'll tell you what. Next
time, I'll take you with me.
What? Do you really mean it?!
I'm going to a secret base.
I've always wanted
to see one in person.
The neighborhood boys
had one when I was a kid,
but they told me
girls weren't allowed.
I can't wait to see it!-
Stop! Kyo, just listen to me!
I don't wanna hear it!
You think it's fun jerking
me around like that?
Now hold on. It wasn't-
okay, it was a little bit fun.
But that's not why I did it!
It was for your own good!
And don't forget,
it was Akito's decision!
Shut up!
I don't give a damn about Akito!
Oh, um... Are you hungry?
I made you some lunch.
Shut up!
Kyo! Don't take
this out on Tohru!
And use the front
door next time!
And take off your shoes!
You're setting
a fine example...
This is the first time
I've seen you in a suit.
It looks good on you!
You don't say?
You look like a butler.
Ah! Lunch is ready!
Yes, but shouldn't
we see about Kyo?
Oh, him? He just needs
to let off some steam.
He's angry that I made
him take an entrance exam.
An entrance exam? For what?
Funny you should ask.
As of today, Kyo is officially
the newest student
at your school...
Oh, and he's going to be
living with us from now on, too.
Don't you take
a single bite. Get out!
Oh well, I had a
feeling you'd be upset...
You see, Kyo pulled a
bit of a vanishing act on us.
He just up and
disappeared for four months...
And do you where
he disappeared to?
He was up on a
mountaintop, training.
What kind of training?
Let me guess.
He's been meditating
under waterfalls
and fighting bears.
Well, I'm not so
sure about that part.
The point is, Kyo
really wants to beat Yuki.
Stupid cat.
So Kyo spent all that
time trying to beat Yuki.
And Yuki really doesn't seem
to like Kyo at all, either.
This is just like the old story.
After the rat tricked the cat,
the cat must have been
angry for a long, long time.
Maybe that's why Yuki
and Kyo don't get along...
I don't know.
And somehow, I get the feeling
he wouldn't want to talk
about it with me...
I wonder if he can
tell us about Yuki!
--He's so cute!
--Not as cute as Yuki!
--Where is he?
--I think he's amazing!
--Oh wow! Oh, my goodness!
--What do you think?
Is he really
Prince Yuki's cousin?
I'll bet he knows
everything about him!
Poor Kyo. He looks so scared.
They're the same.
His electric signals are
exactly the same as Yuki's...
I don't know. But there's
something about them
that's almost inhuman...
Hana, that's just rude.
Oh, hey! Question!
So this new guy is he
really your cousin or what?
Yes, that is the
rumor going around...
I prefer to leave it at that.
Hey, I thought we were talking!
Wait, come back!
What are you doing?!
Oh, Kyo! I don't think
that's a good idea!
Get off me! Let me up!
Leave me alone!!
Amazing! That proves it!
He's definitely
related to Prince Yuki!
I can't believe he jumped.
Hey, aren't you
forgetting about me?
I did just get my
arm ripped off...
That was hysterical!
He looked like a cat trying
to get out of a bath!
Poor Kyo...
He really is like the cat
from the old story, Mom.
He must feel so
alone right now...
But who knows? Maybe... Maybe
one day, we can be friends.
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
But as for me...
I'm going to prove it once and
for all that I'm better than you
and then I'm going
to take my place
as a true member
of this family.
But if you don't keep training
you won't be ready
when that happens.
It will never happen anyway!
I guess that's why
I get so angry with him
because he can't
even see what he has.
He's blinded by
that foolish desire
to join the very same family
I've spent my whole life
trying to run away from.
I hope I'm not prying,
but if there's something
that's bothering you,
you know you can talk to
me about it, if you want.