I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
[Tohru]
Um, Shigure?
I was wondering. Well, May
1st is coming up, and...
would you mind if I
went out that afternoon?
Of course
not. In fact,
I think I'm going out
that afternoon, too...
What is it? Spending some
time with your friends?
Yeah... it's the first
anniversary of Mom's death,
so we're going
to her grave.
Ahh... the first anniversary
of your mother's death.
Uh huh... So, we thought
it might be nice
to pay her a
little visit.
I'm sorry I
can't join you...
Uh? Oh, no, really
that's okay...
[Yuki]
Miss Honda?
Would it be all right
if I came along?
Uh... Oh-- you
don't have to...
Really, I want to... I'd like
to say hello to your mother.
Ah, thanks, it means a lot...
I know it will to Mom, too.
Say, Kyo... If you're not
doing anything that day,
you should think about
going with them...
Ahh... so the Prince is
coming with us... And Kyo?
Well, I don't know...
But I don't think so.
He didn't
say he was.
You know... it's too bad your
mom never got to meet that boy.
She woulda' had so much
fun giving him a hard time.
Hey, it's
an orange!
Dammit,
cut it out!
And I can
see it now.
After Kyo was so angry
he couldn't even speak,
she would grab him, and
give him a hug so tight
that his spine would
snap in two...
That would be terrible!
Well-- for lots of reasons!
Strange... it's been
an entire year...
and still, it's hard
to believe she's gone.
Yeah, I mean I still
keep expecting her
to just show
up one day.
You know, just all
of a sudden, going
"Hi! Sorry, sorry!" With
that big smile of hers...
Ahh, what am
I saying?
That's sure not helping
anything, is it?
Anyway... it only goes
to show just how great
I thought
she was...
The legendary Red Butterfly,
terror of the highway!
I will always treasure
that image of her,
on her lightning-fast
bike, 'popping wheelies'...
A 'popping wheelie'
is an 18-wheeler
with an
oversized belly!
No it's not!
Well, I hope everyone decides
to come... That'd be good.
Yes, it
would.
Hey, if you're goin' to the
grave, then I'm goin' too!
Why are you
telling me?
Shut up! I'm going,
and that's final!
What are you
drawing?!
[Kyo] Sorta' small,
for a temple.
It's nice, isn't it? Just
a quiet little place.
It's kind of
like home...
That's a weird thing
to say, but all right...
Oh! Did that sound weird?
What I meant was--
Forget I
said anything.
[Yuki]
You know...
I'm glad to see we have
such a nice day today.
I'd say we're
pretty fortunate,
as bad as the
weather's been lately.
[Tohru] Yeah... it's like
Mom's smiling down on us...
After all... She has
a lot to smile about.
The two of you are
coming to visit.
[Uo] Tohru!
Hey! Great day for
visiting a grave, huh?!
Yes!
[Kyo] What the hell
are you wearing?
What do
you mean?
We're wearing black.
What did you expect?
Not that!
Miss Uotani... that
outfit you're wearing...
well, is that
a... trenchcoat?
Hm? Yeah, pretty
sharp huh?
I inherited this from
Kyoko, back in the day.
You are
looking at
the legendary "Red
Butterfly's" riding jacket!
Uh... "Red
Butterfly"?
That's what they used to call
Mom when she was in her gang!
In her gang? And
that's a good thing?
All right! Everybody's here!
Let's get this party started!
[Both] They're... they're
actually having fun...
That's
weird.
It's already
been cleaned up.
Guess somebody got
here before us.
It must've
been Grandfather!
He's the only other
person I can think of
who knows Mom's
favorite food!
[Kyo] Your
grandfather?
Yoo-hoooo!
Oh yeah, him.
[Tohru]
Uh-huh!
Which side of the family
did you say he was from?
Oh uh, he's my grandfather
on my father's side.
Yeah, Kyoko
and her parents
weren't exactly on
speaking terms...
Your father...
how did he...
He got sick, and just
couldn't get better...
That's what
Mom told me...
I was so
small then...
I don't really remember
too much about him...
Hello, Mom... I
came to see you.
We all came.
I guess your grandfather
already did all the cleaning,
but we can still put
these flowers up, huh?
Uh-huh.
Her father died... And
then she lost her mother...
So, how
is it she--
...how is it, after all
the tragedies in her life,
she's still able to
smile like she does?
I remember the day
of the accident...
One of the teachers came and
called her out of class...
They talked in the
door for a minute...
and then they
ran out...
Her two friends went
running after her.
For a little while, everyone
in class was silent.
I remember thinking
at the time...
"Maybe someone in her
family's been hurt"...
...but it was just
a passing thought.
Back then, I barely
even realized she existed.
She was just one of
the girls in class.
The one called
"Tohru Honda".
How could I have
known that one day,
we would be living
in the same house...
that we'd get to know one
another like we have...
[Tohru] Yuki!
Did you see?
Aren't these
pretty flowers?
Or that, whenever
she smiled, somehow,
I'd find myself
smiling with her...
[Tohru] Okay,
it's all ready!
Tohru! This
is wonderful!
You can't have a
picnic on a grave!
Huh? What's
the big deal?
C'mon, Kyoko
will like it
if we make a little
noise before we leave!
So what if the temple
people see you?
So what if
they do?
This isn't
exactly... normal.
[Uo] Look, just quit
complaining and sit down.
You don't expect to eat
standing up, do you?
That's not good
for you, you know.
[Tohru] Kyo, do you want
me to make you a plate?
[Kyo] Whatever...
[Tohru] Okay!
So, Miss Uotani, I
get the impression
you were close with
Miss Honda's mother?
Oh yeah, she was
a great friend...
But you know,
she was my idol
way before we ever
met. She was a legend.
What do you
mean, a legend?
[Uo] Like I said! The
legendary "Red Butterfly"!
[Kyo] Like I said! What're
you talkin' about?!
This is
delicious...
See, they say whenever
Kyoko rode her bike,
all you'd see were
her taillights
just flash
right by you,
like a red butterfly
tearing ass into the night!
[Kyo] How do taillights
look like a butterfly?
[Uo] What?! You
gotta' be kidding!
Don't you have
any imagination
in that big orange
head of yours?
[Kyo] Shut up! I don't have
to take that from you!
[Uo] Oh, is that a
fact, Orange Top?!
[Kyo] Rrrrrrrrgh!
I can see it... How
hard she's been trying.
The fact that Tohru can smile
like this after only a year...
I can only imagine the
effort it must have taken
for her to lift
herself up
under the weight
of her grief...
I... I don't think... If
someone close to me died,
as close as Tohru
was to her mother...
I don't think I would be
able to find the strength
to smile again
so soon...
For example, if something were
to happen to Tohru tomorrow,
the pain would be so
unbearable that I wonder if
I might begin to wish that
I had never even met her,
if it might be
easier to forget...
Sweet Tohru...
...you have
tried so hard.
But even so... I'm gonna
guess that smile of hers
has at least something
to do with those two...
I mean just
look at 'em...
I dunno, the three of
them just really seem
to belong together
in some weird way...
Yes, that's
true...
You do know... it's bound
to happen one day...
one of em's gonna'
tell her he likes her...
Oh, no, no... I'm afraid
I simply could not allow
my Tohru to date either
one of those boys...
So, what? Are you
her mother now?
Well, I really only
meant that half-joking...
So you were
half-serious...
It's their
signals...
I can still sense something
that troubles me...
There are many
conflicting emotions,
hanging like dark clouds
around their hearts...
I suppose that's true of every
person, to some extent...
But with those two, it seems
to be rather extreme...
And as long as those
dark clouds remain...
I'm not sure they
can ever truly share
their hearts
with another...
Then again, perhaps
I'm worrying too much...
They both seem pretty clueless
when it comes to dating...
Well, I'd say that goes
double for Tohru...
But, you
never know...
Sometimes, I bet
even clueless people
manage to fall
in love...
Oh, no... Picture our little
Tohru as a new bride...
Just thinking about it,
it makes me want to cry...
Okay. You're gettin' a
little bit ahead of yourself,
don't you
think?
Ahh... There's nothing
better than relaxing
with a cup of hot tea at
the end of a long day...
And especially after we
had such a nice visit!
I'm really glad I finally
got to introduce you
to Yuki and Kyo
today, Mom...
I can't even begin
to tell you...
Those two... they both
take such good care of me.
Maybe someday soon,
I'll get a chance to introduce
you to Shigure, too...
I really have found a
wonderful home here,
living in this house,
together with all of them.
And I'm so grateful for
every day I've had here...
So, Mom... I just
want you to know,
that while you're up
there watching over me,
you don't have to
worry any more...
I'm home.
Thanks so much for coming to
visit with me yesterday...
Hey... C'mon, we should
be thanking you...
Especially for all
the food you made...
Yes,
Tohru...
Your cooking keeps getting
better and better...
You're going to make
a fine bride one day...
I'm going
to cry...
Tohru!
Hide me!
Momiji!
We're playing cops and
robbers! And I'm the robber!
Momiji! Give it
up! You're busted!
They found me!
Gotta run!
Be careful! Watch
where you're going!
Hey! He's gettin' away!
Come on you guys! Let's go!
We've got you
now, Momiji!
You're goin'
downtown!
We've got you
surrounded!
How 'bout
that.
It looks
like fun.
Be... Be
careful...
But I don't know why they're
calling it 'Cops and Robbers'.
It just looked like a bunch of
boys chasing a girl to me...
He must look like
his mother...
[Uo] Oh... yeah... that's
what they say, isn't it?
Guys look like their moms and
girls look like their dads?
Yes, just like Tohru
resembles her father
more than
her mother...
Well, more like her
grandfather maybe...
Now that I'm thinking
about it, Momiji's parents
didn't come to the entrance
ceremony, did they?
The white-haired boy's
parents didn't come either...
Oh... I guess
they didn't...
Actually, I've never even heard
Momiji mention his parents.
None of the Sohmas talk
about their parents much...
This looks heavy! Can
I help you with it?
Momiji! What are
you doing here?
Oh, well... this
is Papa's building.
Ah! I see, so I
guess that means
your father works here
somewhere, is that right?
Sort of... but
not really.
Okay, I'll
tell you...
Ah, good...
There you are...
We didn't know if
you were still here...
The president's been looking
everywhere for you...
'kay... Tell him I'm going
home in just a minute,
so there's nothing
to worry about.
Right...
President? Looking
for Momiji?
See, this is just one of the
buildings that Papa owns!
That's what you
meant?! I had no idea!
Here...
Look!
Ta-da!
This is your father?
He's very handsome!
Oh, yeah, that
one's Mama.
Wow. She's
very beautiful...
Yep!
And she has such a
kind-looking face...
Her and Papa... well, Papa's
a Sohma so he's from here,
and he met her while
he was off at college.
Then they
got married.
That's
the story!
I still don't
know how Papa
managed to find
such a hot... Mama!
Know what? I have a
little sister, too!
Her name's Momo. And she
looks just like Mama!
I can't believe it! Momiji,
you have a younger sister?!
Yeah! She
just started
her second year of
elementary school.
Oh, and she's not a
member of the zodiac...
But still... she's really cute!
And she's still just a baby!
She follows Mama
around everywhere
she goes like
a baby chick.
And it's still hard for
her to say some words,
so when
she talks,
it's usually this
cute little mumble...
It's adorable!
Really!
I've never seen
him look so happy!
Her and Mama... on most days
they come to pick up Papa!
Mm! And it's
almost time!
Oh, so then all of you will
be going home together?
Well, no... but it'd
be great if we could!
You see, Mama doesn't
exactly know who I am...
Oh, Momiji...
What are you doing here?
And especially at this hour?
[Tohru] Ohh... we were
just talking about her...
And now,
here she is!
So then... This little
girl... must be Momo!
It really is
like Hana said.
Momiji does look
like his mother...
Ehh... My friend has
a part-time job here...
So I thought I'd stop
and play for a while.
Mama doesn't exactly
know who I am...
Is that so? Well,
I hardly think
this is a place
to play...
You're right!
I'm sorry.
Well... You really
shouldn't be out this late.
Your mother must be
worried sick about you!
[Momiji] Yes, I know. I
was just about to go back.
All right, be sure
you go straight home.
Keep up the
good work.
Oh! Uh,
thank you...
Momo... Let's go now...
We can't keep Papa waiting!
Awww... I really didn't
want her to see me...
Now I'm gonna have to
apologize to Papa...
Um, Momiji...?
Yeah...
Like I said, Mama doesn't know
about me... She forgot...
Her memory
was erased...
She knows I'm a member
of the Sohma family,
but she thinks I'm
someone else's son...
Did you know, children
cursed by the zodiac,
when they're born,
they're always born
two months premature...
Imagine what that
was like for her...
She'd been married to
the man she truly loved...
they were having their
first child together...
She must have been so worried
when the baby came early...
And then,
after all that,
the first time she tried
to hold that baby...
to see it change into
a strange animal...
How horrifying would that be
to a new mother? Any mother...
I know now that when
a mother has a child
who is cursed by
the zodiac...
often, she will feel
either the need
to be overly
protective of it,
or she will reject
it completely...
Mama is one of the ones
who rejected her child...
She rejected me with
her entire body...
It got to the point
that she couldn't even
stand to
look at me...
Sometimes she
would just snap--
yelling, screaming...
at everything...
Thinking about
it now...
I guess it was just like...
what happened to Kana.
Momiji...
Mama is very,
very sick...
But if she were to
forget about you...
they say she might
get better...
I know this is painful
for you too, Momiji...
But Papa will love
you twice as much
to make up
for her love...
If you love Mama,
like I do... Momiji,
help us
save her...
Is this
what you want?
Do you really want to
forget about your only child?
Are you sure... you
won't regret it?
Right now, my
greatest regret...
Is that that thing ever
came out of my body...
And so, I was erased
from Mama's memory...
and like they said, she
steadily began to get better...
After the first
couple months,
she even started
smiling again...
I guess what I did...
I guess it saved her...
[Tohru] So...
all this time...
he's been watching her
from a distance...
trying not to let her see
him... just like today...
But you know? There's
something I believe...
I want to try and
live my life,
carrying all of my
memories with me...
And even if those
memories are painful...
Even if they do
nothing but hurt me...
I want to
keep them...
Even those memories I sometimes
wish I could forget...
As long as I carry
them with me...
as long as I can keep
holding on, then someday...
Someday, I'll be
strong enough
that those memories
don't hurt me anymore...
and I'll be glad
I have them...
That's what I believe...
with all of my heart.
That's why all of my
memories are precious to me.
I don't think it would be
okay to forget a single one...
And that's why...
the truth is...
I didn't really want Mama to
forget about me... I didn't.
What I wanted... was
for her to hold on...
But I guess that was
selfish of me...
It'll be
our secret?
Me too...
I believe
that, too!
[Tohru] All of
my memories...
I want to keep them
close to my heart...
And I want to go
on believing...
I'm going to
hold on...
no matter how hard it
might be sometimes...
I never want
to forget.
Because, someday... I
will be strong enough...
All of the memories
that are painful now...
they won't
hurt anymore...
...and when that
day comes,
I'll be glad that
I have them...
Yes, all of my memories
are precious to me...
Every single one...
Now let's all gather,
Enjoying the company we share,
Our tears will dissolve
into thin air,
As we drink up
this wonderful life.
La, la, la...
Takin' in all the
sweet love and life.
La, la, la...
Drinkin' up all this
good love and life.
La, la, la...
Take it in all this
sweet love and life.
[Shigure] Alright,
here's an idea.
What do you say we
go on a trip tomorow?
After all this
is Golden Week.
It would be a shame if we
didn't do something special.
Chances like this
don't come very often.
At any rate, I thought we might
go to one of the Sohma's spas
or perhaps
the lake house.
How does that
sound Tohru?
[Tohru] But I've already been
on a trip to the Hot Springs...
I couldn't go on another
one. It would be too much.
[Shigure] And what a lovely
trip that must have been...
It's too bad I wasn't
able to be there.
I did so want to go...
but now I guess I'll never
get to take a trip with you.