I was so happy when you smiled,
Your smile breaks
through the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny days
that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again,
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain,
You can go on living as
much as your heart believes.
You can't be born again
although you can change.
Let's stay together always.
Don't look at me!
[Akito] I've never seen
anything so ugly...
And that
smell... awful...
It smells like something
dead and rotting...
It's the cat's
evil spirit...
This is its
true form...
It's disgusting.
K- Kyo...?
She saw me... She
saw me... She saw me!
It's over now... It's all
over! There's no hope!
[Kazuma] And so, you have
seen Kyo's other form...
The one he has kept
hidden from you.
It is part of the burden
he bears as the Cat,
that he is also cursed to
take this grotesque shape...
Do you find
it revolting?
Is it...
frightening... to you?
Please...
Kyo...
Kyo...?
Kyo... Kyo!
[Akito] What's this...?
Tohru Honda...?
But what are you doing out
here? Is something wrong?
Aw... How
awful...
It serves you
right, you know...
What do you really
know about the Sohmas?
Do you think
you understand
what it means to
be cursed? Do you?
I only have a short
time left to live...
Nothing can
change that...
I alone carry the full
weight of the Zodiac Curse.
So you see... I
do understand.
I wonder what it was that
everyone expected of you?
Did they really think
you would be able to
miraculously
save us, somehow?
You deserve
this pain...
But don't think this
will be the end of it...
I'm going to
make you regret
you were ever
involved with us...
I will make you suffer,
the way we suffer.
[Shigure]
Akito!
Awww...
Now thanks to you, I'm
completely soaked...
Tohru...
I--
I'm sorry...
I... I
thought--
No, I knew...
I knew...
Tohru...
Let's end
this! End it!
I know... I know
it's painful...
But you
can...
[Kagura] Yuki... why
didn't you go after him?
Do you... Do you still
hate Kyo that much?
I've always hated
him. My entire life.
He's the cat
and I'm the rat.
We were born hating
each other...
That's the way
it's always been,
and that's the way
it'll always be.
I wonder... Who decided
it had to be that way?
It's sad,
isn't it.
And what about you, Kagura?
Aren't you going after him?
No, I'm not... I've
made up my mind.
Kyo already knows I accept
him, no matter what...
and no matter what
form he's in...
I mean, there isn't another
girl in the whole world
who loves him as
much as I do...
Which is why... I know
that I can't help him...
Right now, the only
one who can help...
the person he needs
the most, is Tohru...
Kagura...
I'm a member of the
zodiac, the same as him...
so for me to go
to him now...
it wouldn't give
him any comfort.
He needs to be accepted
by someone else...
Someone who doesn't
share our curse...
And so... all I can do is
leave things up to Tohru.
Huh... That's
strange... Huh?--
Ah! No, that's not
it... Hmm... Let's see...
Ah... Here it is...
Kyo's
color...
The boy didn't
even cry.
His mother's
funeral, not a tear...
If only she hadn't given birth
to a child cursed by the Cat...
Maybe she'd still be with us...
Maybe she wouldn't have--
Shut up! It's not my
fault! It's not my fault!
That's right...
I know...
It's nice to meet you...
My name is Kazuma Sohma.
It's not my fault!
It's all
right...
I know...
Kyo...
If you'd like, why don't
you come live with me?
I know I may
not look it,
but I am the instructor
of a karate dojo.
I'd be happy to teach you,
if you have any interest.
Look,
it's Kyo!
So, Kazuma is really
taking him in, huh?
That's how it looks... You
know, I'm sure he means well,
but still, I feel
sorry for him.
And he's still
so young, too!
What was he thinking, adopting
a boy cursed by the Cat!
It's all right,
Kyo... From now on,
we'll be breathing the air
from a higher place...
Say... So, you're
a "master" right?
On TV, they said
a karate teacher
was called a
"master"...
So that means you're
a master, right?
Haha! Well, I suppose that
may be true... But...
I've never asked any of my
students to call me that.
[Student 1] Ha, ha, ha!
Watch out, Teacher!
I'm gonna be as good as
you one of these days!
[Kazuma]
Well, there is no doubt.
Both of you have
improved quite a bit.
[Student 1]
You really think so?
Thanks, Teacher, you
just made my day!
[Student 2]
By the way, Teacher.
When do you think we'll have
our next rank advancement test?
Master?
Welcome
home... Kyo...
Did you even try to
settle the issue
before resorting
to violence?
All he did was make a
comment about your hair.
Your father
is on his way.
Although, I'm
forced to wonder
how his father
is raising him...
Still, I feel
sorry for him.
What was he thinking, adopting
a boy cursed by the Cat!
...he's not
my dad...
Master, you're not
my dad! You're not!
It's all
right...
...a higher
place...
Welcome
home... Kyo...
All I wanted, was
to make amends...
Like Kyo, my grandfather
was also cursed by the cat...
For this, he was
treated as an outcast,
alienated by his
entire family.
The pariah of
the Sohma clan.
And
so...
I only met my grandfather
one time... By chance.
Come over here, Kazuma...
Let me give you some candy.
Uh! No way! I don't
wanna be cursed!
I said such cruel
words to him...
I see...
But his kindness was
greater than my own.
He only smiled at me, as
if to say, "I forgive you."
Soon after that, my
grandfather passed away.
And as I
grew older,
I was able to see many of the
things I couldn't as a child.
I began to
understand
the torment he had
been forced to endure...
The foolishness...
The cruelty...
And I could see that, since
my grandfather's time,
none of this
had changed.
Kyo, If you'd like, why
don't you come live with me?
That Kyo was now forced to lead
the same life of suffering...
And so, I took him
in, to make amends
for my family's cruelty...
Or so I told myself.
Though, perhaps what
I really wanted
was to ease my own
feelings of guilt.
However, over time... as we
passed our days together...
as I watched him beginning
to grow and change...
...Before I even
realized it...
A genuine bond had
formed between us...
And every time I
saw him smile,
I could feel that bond
growing stronger...
He became dear to me.
I cared for him. I worried.
I wanted him to have all
the happiness in the world...
In many ways, I felt as though
I had become his father.
And now... I have
perhaps shown him
the greatest
cruelty of all.
I have ignored his feelings
and taken his beads...
I've forced him to
endure this torment...
You're not my dad!
Kyo...
[Uo] So what's
the deal?
I don't get why this was so
urgent, all of a sudden...
I mean, could've just
come here tomorrow.
With Tohru, even...
[Hana] I just...
sense something...
[Uo] You and your
electric waves...
Oh, well,
we're here...
Kyoko's gonna be pretty
surprised to see us, huh?
I mean, comin' here in the
middle of the night like--
Tohru?
What are you doing out here?
You're soaked to the bone!
Uo... H-
Hana...
Are you okay?
What happened?!
I... I can't go back... I don't
belong there... I never did...
I don't belong
there, with them...
in that house...
I don't--
Tohru...? It's
okay. Just tell me--
Don't!
What the hell
was that for?!
You can't comfort
Tohru right now!
That's what the electric
signals are telling me!
What are you
talking about?
Go... Tohru... there's
somewhere you need to be...
You have to go!
I can't...
I just can't!
Get up...!
Tohru... GET UP!
I can't go...
Stop it, Hana!
Tohru...
I'm here...
Damn you...!
STAND UP!
Hana!
Let me go!
Tohru!
Go now! Hurry!
There's something
you have to do...
You're the only one who
can! You know I'm right...
What the hell does
that mean?! Hana!
This isn't something we can
help you with... We can't...!
All we can do, is
tell you to go...!
So hurry up!
Go! Go!
Tohru...?
Tohru...
[Uo] But why...?
[Uo] WHY...?!
I was so happy
when you smiled,
Your smile breaks through
the clouds of grey,
Far from the sunny
days that lie in sleep.
Waiting with patience
for the Spring,
when the flowers will
bloom renewed again
knowing there's more
beyond the pain of today.
Although the scars
of yesterday remain...