At noon you have the
company's regular meeting.
And then at two o'clock,
your dance lesson with
Mrs. Hyatt begins...
Followed by your
political studies lesson
with Professor Macmillan...
That's all you have
for today, my lord.
Fine.
One more thing.
We received this.
"On behalf of the Count Alois
Trancy, I write this day
to apologize for my master's
discourtesy at the ball
the other day and request
your most honored presence
at the ball to be held here
at the Trancy Mansion
tomorrow afternoon
at four o'clock."
Alois Trancy...
I will kill you.
Incidents in the English
underworld which most greatly
offend the Queen are judged in
darkness by the Phantomhive
family, the
"Queen's guard dogs."...
They are then erased in
darkness by the Trancy family,
the "Queen's spiders."
Both houses had the
Queen's trust as her
"villainous nobles"...
However, that distinction was
not enough for Alois Trancy.
Seeking to monopolize
Her Majesty's favor,
Alois spread the rumor that
the Phantomhive guard dog
was possessed by a demon.
At the time, the previous
head of the Phantomhives
was investigating a series
of mysterious
spontaneous combustions.
Alois alleged that the
crimes were the result
of Phantomhive's
demonic possession...
And so...
He took it upon himself
to purge them...
...under the guise
of "exorcism."
Subsequently, Alois and
his butler destroyed
all evidence of
their involvement.
Records indicate that the spider
either erased peoples' pasts
or replaced them
with false ones.
They went to great lengths in
order to cover up their crime.
Yes, I received my orders
from Lord Trancy...
He told me to burn down
the Phantomhive manor...
and that I should sell off
the surviving child.
Spare my life, I beg you!
Through your actions,
you have damaged my pride...
and now you'll
atone with your death.
Alois...
you were behind it all...
for what you've done
I will kill you, too...
This time you'll
dance to my tune.
The "Dance Macabre."
The Dance of Death...
Indeed.
At least they have spared us the
trouble of inviting them here.
Let's prepare ourselves,
Sebastian...
It's time to duel.
Very good, master.
In that case, allow me to
alter the schedule slightly...
We'll attend the company
meeting as per usual.
I'll have your lessons
with Mrs. Hyatt
and Professor Macmillan
rescheduled for tomorrow,
at the earliest...
Today at four o'clock,
we will attend the ball.
And we shall fight to the death
with the house of Trancy.
Ciel!
I'm so glad you came.
Welcome!
Good afternoon, Lord Trancy.
It's most excellent
to see you, my lord.
Come with me...
We're holding a special party
in your honor.
What's this?
It appears to be
a dueling arena.
Here's an idea, Ciel.
Let's have our
butlers do the work.
They can dance in our places.
Whoever can keep dancing
the longest will
be declared the winner...
And the loser will have
to follow any orders
given by the victor...
What do you say, Ciel.
Do we have a deal, then?
We weren't alone in
our thinking, master.
It seems they've planned
a death match as well.
This sounds like exactly the
sort of party I had in mind...
I much prefer it to dressing up
in silly costumes anyway.
Sebastian, this is an order...
Win, and bring Alois Trancy
to stand before me.
But don't kill him.
I will take care
of that matter personally.
Yes indeed...
my young master.
Your Highness...
what are your orders?
Hmm...?
Ah...
I want you to make
Ciel Phantomhive mine.
And I want Sebastian Michaelis
to experience exquisite agony.
You can see to that,
can't you Claude?
Oh yes...
Your Highness.
We dance.
Be still my beating heart.
C'est tres fantastique!
It's unbelievable...!
An ancient dueling arena
where legendary heroes
fought to the death...!
Oh!
This is tonight's ball...?
I am honored...
Never in my life have
I felt such excitement
to receive a party invitation!
Pardon, sir...
Might I inquire what brings you
to the mansion today?
Oh yes...
I am pleased to be attending
the Trancy costume ball...
I'm Aleister Chambers,
Viscount Druitt.
I'm afraid the costume ball
was last week, sir...
This afternoon's event
is a private affair...
for Earl Phantomhive alone.
Oh, good heavens...!
How could I have
mixed up the dates?
I'll just go home then...
But why did no one remark
upon my absence last week...?
Being a criminal really does
lower one's station in society.
A visage as clear as a lake's
surface...! If you but held
a steely-grey knife,
you could be one of
Valhalla's valkaryies...!
But no...!
Your dusky elegance and the
bandages covering your face
are better suited to
a beautiful demoness.
How satisfying.
You've proven yourself every
bit as clever as you look.
A dagger?
It's part of the
entertainment for the ball.
A party filled with blood-lust
and fraught with danger,
how exquisite!
I, Druitt, have ever served
the goddess of beauty.
I insist upon observing the
afternoon's events for myself.
Finally...
the stage is set
for our dance.
So begins the Danse Macabre.
Group attack...
Enjoy "The Bloody Washtub!"
A three-pronged attack with a
dagger, a long-range weapon,
and a projectile weapon.
Oh my!
Group attack: transition
from "Bloody Washtub"
to "Cursed Vanity Mirror."
And now they all charge as one!
Your battle moves are as
well aligned as your faces.
Here you go.
Now you can be
together forever.
Oh my!
Good show!
Bother...
Now I'll have to go to
the trouble of mending this.
No need for that.
You'll be full
of holes soon enough.
So much power!
I see what you mean...
This certainly does seem to be
a very holey opportunity.
I shall make every effort
to repay you in kind...
for every last bullet.
That will do for now...
It's time for our tea.
My goodness...
Has it already gotten so late?
As I'm sure you
understand, I must see
to my master's refreshments.
We'll suspend
the match for now.
Of course...
May I make use of
your kitchen as well?
Desirable souls.
Luscious souls.
If souls do very in taste.
Then one, obsessively
pursued by a demon.
The soul like that
of Ciel Phantomhive.
Oh, do excuse me.
It's just the way you were
looking at my master
was beginning to concern me.
I had the strangest feeling
that you were assessing
the flavor of his soul.
Make other dinner plans...
You won't lay a finger
on my master's soul...
Or give him any lip.
Ooh...!
Bravo!
Well, that was just
a whole lot of pointless.
This afternoon we have puits
d'amor, crème pâtissière,
and raspberry jam in a
pastry made of pie dough.
To accompany, we have
a delicately brewed
Mariage Frères Eros tea.
Th...
th-th-th...
this...
is amazing!
The puits d'amour pairs rich
cream with the tartness
of raspberry in a satiny
ensemble so rare it seems
like water in the desert.
I thirst for more!
Without another taste,
I shall be forever banished
to the dusty Sahara
of the palate...
I beg you, my intrepid desert
guide, please show me
the path to the oasis!
Here we have a forêt noire...
This treat is comprised of
layers of chocolate sponge cake
and cherry compote finished with
a dressing of white cream.
And with it we have a pot of
superfine Keemun tea shipped
in from the Qing Empire.
Fine.
Tr-Tr-Tr-Tr...
tr-tr...
Très bien!
This forêt noire combines
the rich aroma of chocolate
with the tart scent of cherry.
The flavors surge forth
like ocean waves,
landing on your tongue
with an overwhelming splash...
I would follow this taste
around the globe...!
I would happily circumnavigate
the world to explore
its every exquisite nuance...
Conquistador of afternoon tea,
please show me the way!
Such a dilemma...
How can I choose
which is better...?
I can't do it...!
I can't do it...! I must
go powder my nose!
The water closet
is that way, sir.
That man is certifiable.
Now, then...
let us resume.
Indeed.
Shall we dance?
Dance we shall...
But first...
Are you certain?
All right.
What's he doing?
Goodness, look at that.
The ancient sword Lavateinn and
its curse of eternal darkness.
I never dreamed you
had such a fine article.
Naturally.
I thought your invitation
to dance deserved
a suitably grand response.
And now...
the Danse Macabre.
What do you think
of Claude's sword?
Impressive, eh?
I'll admit it does seem
to be a fine weapon.
Perhaps you could give
me a little tour
of the Trancy manor...
If it isn't any trouble.
Do you need the
loo as well...?
I'll show you the way.
Well, master...
I'm disappointed in you for
running off and leaving
the fight to your
butler like this.
I'm disappointed in you
for letting your eyes wander.
You know...
Your obsession with that
human's soul is getting you
into trouble...
I think it's beginning to dull
your demon instincts.
Oh, dear...
now how did that happen?
Ciel...
What is this?
Where are you going?
I've seen enough of
their silly performance.
Alois, Earl Trancy.
You have crossed a line.
You have robbed me
of my pride and have
disgraced and demeaned me.
I cannot accept this...
Thus, here and now,
I challenge you to a duel.
Oh, so you didn't just
want me to come in here
and piss with you?
These are the spider
threads of Trancy House.
They can cut through steel.
One careless movement and...
off with your head.
Just what I would
expect of a spider.
That's much better.
I feel quite
marvelously refreshed.
I've never actually had the
opportunity to duel before...
How do we proceed?
You'll have to tell me.
We stand back to back
and then begin walking
at the call of "allez."...
We pivot on the tenth step
and the duel begins.
Simple enough...
Sounds fun.
Let's do it.
Great Scott,
a real, live duel!
Allez...!
One...
two...
three...
four...
fi--
Now, now, let's not
have any cheating.
Why, you!
You always lose
your temper so quickly...
Come; let's enjoy our dance!
Here we are,
Sebastian Michaelis.
Young master...
That's it...!
One, two, three...
One, two three...
Down you go!
Here we are, Ciel.
You'll finally be mine.
Sebastian wants so very
badly to devour your soul.
But he won't get to...
because, you see, I am going
to tear your soul to shreds
and feed it to the
spiders of my mansion...
Poor thing.
I know it's going
to irritate him terribly.
This is going to be
a lot of fun.
The soul of the queen's
guard dog isn't cheap...
A trifling little spider
like you could never
afford a taste...
But if you don't mind
having your legs ripped off,
then by all means, try it.
I see you still have enough
energy to be cheeky.
It's useless to keep
struggling...
Just give up and submit to me!
Submit?
I'm the one who has you.
Master!
How horrific!
Please, help me Claude!.
Help me!
I'm dying!
Yes...
--Your High--
--Hold, Sebastian.
Until I've killed him,
stay back!
Very good, my young lord.
Die...
Alois Trancy.
Wait, please...!
I don't want to die...
It hurts...
please spare me, Ciel.
You're truly pathetic, Alois...
You killed my parents, and
you want me to spare you?!
Wait!
No, listen to me!
You don't understand...
You're being
tricked by a demon!
I'm telling you, believe me!
A demon?
My parents were
killed too, you know...
My family was burned to death
along with the whole village...
Someone stole them from me!
Can't you see that we're
basically the same...?
I promise, I won't
bother you anymore.
I'll apologize for everything...
Just please...
please spare me.
Please let me live!
Through your actions you
have damaged my pride...
and now you'll
atone with your death.
Please hurry, Claude.
Help me!
You saved me!
Let go, bastard!
Young master!
It's not over...!
I'll kill you!
Given the current circumstances,
I'm afraid I can't allow
this dance to continue...
Terribly sorry, but I believe
we'll have to excuse ourselves
for the remainder of the day.
Do you hear me, Claude?
Oh yes, of course...
I understand...
Another time, then.
Master, I suggest
we be on our way.
Now, first you run off...
Then you get yourself hurt...
I'm positively at
my wit's end with you, my lord.
Do you really hate
dancing that much?
Put me down, Sebastian!
Honestly now sir, how can you
possibly have the energy to
throw a temper tantrum like this
after losing all that blood?
It's the day of
a ball, after all...
Come now...
We'll dance our way,
into the sunset.
What happens when a soul is
obsessively pursued by a demon?
Claude...
what are you looking at?
Come on, do something!
Can't you see I've been
stabbed...? Quickly!
Help me, please!
He traded his soul for
a demon's power...
yet revenge only means
something to him if he wins
it with his own hand.
He knows blood and
death and darkness...
but still, his soul is pure...
untainted...
immaculate.
What is it, Claude?
Day into night...
pleasure into pain...
this chance encounter...
into ecstasy.
Hoheo taralna, rondero tarel!
Hoheo taralna,
rondero tarel...!
Hoheo taralna, ron--
You look like you're staring at
maggots swarming on a pile of--
Introducing Jim Macken...
A grubby little urchin
with blond ringlets...
angelic hair in
such contradiction
to his lowly soul...
He found a new
name for himself...
Now meet Alois Trancy.
Next time: "Divulging Butler" If
I couldn't whisper a few words
of love here and there...
well...
what kind of
a butler would I be?