Here we are, dear...
This is the Phantomhive manor.
It's always a pleasure
to see you, Lady...
Please, do come inside.
Thank you, Sebastian.
Ciel!
We've been expecting you...
Allow me, miss.
Here he is, dear...
Presenting Ciel,
Earl Phantomhive...!
Ciel, this is the new friend I
mentioned to you in my letter...
We met at a ball last month, and
I took an instant liking to her.
And I felt sure you'd
adore her as much as I do.
I could not wait
to introduce you,
so I brought her
along this afternoon.
What's an earl
to do with you?
Welcome to my estate, miss.
I'm Ciel, the head of
Phantomhive household...
I hope you'll find tonight's
ball an enjoyable experience.
Sebastian, see that she
has everything she needs.
Certainly, my lord...
Pleased to make
your acquaintance...
Sebastian Michaelis,
butler to the Phantomhives.
I am at your service...
We pride ourselves
on hospitality...
We shall offer every comfort.
And now...
welcome to Phantomhive Manor.
We have prepared
this guest room for you.
Lovely, you say...?
Thank you...
I'm so pleased.
Over the generations, the
Phantomhives have furnished
this room with the finest
quality historic pieces.
You will find that everything
is suitable for a gentlewoman,
so please do make
yourself at home.
I see you admiring the
photographs on the mantle...
They are of the previous
earl, Vincent Phantomhive,
and his lovely wife, Rachel.
From what I understand,
they were prominent figures,
much loved by the
entire community.
They devoted themselves
passionately to worthy
civil causes such as aiding the
poor and improving medical care
and infrastructure.
The Queen evidently placed a
great deal of trust in them...
You might ask my master
for further details
at tea this afternoon.
For now, please
make yourself --
If you'll please wait here...
There's a matter
I must attend to.
I suppose I shouldn't
be surprised.
It's this bloody
new burner we got.
The blasted thing won't work!
Please, miss, stay back.
My deepest apologies...
Are you injured?
That was a close shave, eh?
We came pretty near to startin'
a bloody great fire in there.
You did start a fire!
Are you all right...?
sorry, Sebastian...
Hello and who is this?
Miss?
Our visitor is a friend
of the Lady Elizabeth...
She will be one of our esteemed
guests at this evening's ball.
Oh my...!
How lovely!
It's always exciting
to have a fancy new guest!
And she's a right pretty
little thing, isn't she?
I'm terribly sorry you
had to witness that scene,
even more so that you
were exposed to danger...
I can't possibly
apologize enough.
However, I do recall requesting
that you wait for me here...
Every household has its
secrets--certain places that
are not meant to be
seen by visitors.
Strolling, uninvited,
about somebody else's manor
strikes me as
quite inconsiderate.
However...
I certainly understand
the curiosity of the young...
Ah, I see.
It's your first visit
to such a large estate...
and your inquisitive
nature got the best of you...
Rather similar to an innocent
puppy who knows no fear.
We still have
a little time before tea...
I'd be honored if you'd allow me
to show you around the manor.
We can assuage your curiosity.
Then with your permission,
I shall be your escort
for a guided tour...
May I take your hand?
Just in here, we have
the recreation room...
As you can see,
it is furnished with
a billiard table and
other gaming equipment,
as well as many of the
Funtom Company's products...
Our goal is to provide guests
with ample entertainment.
My...
who have we here...?
It isn't much, I know,
but do make yourself
comfortable.
As you can see, the
recreation room is furnished
with a billiard table and
other gaming equipment,
as well as many of the
Funtom Company's products...
Our goal is to provide guests
with ample entertainment...
Please come take a seat.
I'm sure you
will enjoy yourself.
Thank you for such a detailed
explanation of the room...
Though I must say
it sounds familiar,
as if I've heard
it somewhere before.
If you please...
this man is Mr. Lau,
head of the English branch
of the Chinese trading
company Kunlun...
Mr. Lau, this is a friend
of Lady Elizabeth's.
She will be attending
the ball tonight.
Some advice, miss:
be careful...
Phantomhive Manor
is absolutely crawling
with dangerous beasties...
You wouldn't want to be
eaten by one, now would you?
May I present
to you our library,
the pride of the
Phantomhive estate.
The family heads have gathered
books for generations...
The result is
a library comparable
to those at any university--
Brilliant timing...!
I was growing ever so bored.
Please Prince Soma, we're in
the middle of your studies.
Agni...!
Everyone needs
a rest now and then.
And from what
I can see, it seems you
were studying
quite diligently.
Yes.
A friend of Lady Elizabeth's
is visiting today for tea...
She will also be attending
the ball later this evening.
Is this her, Sebastian?
Miss, please allow me to
introduce you to a friend
of my master's, the twenty-sixth
child of the king of Bengal,
Prince Soma Asman Kadar, and
his very capable butler Agni.
Namaste ji.
Prince Soma, Agni, this is--
So beautiful!
Sire?
Oh...!
Hello miss, I'm Prince Soma...
I fancied you immediately...
Would you like to be
my handmaiden...?
Or, if you prefer...
my...
my wife.
Oh, Prince Soma...! At
last...! You've finally found
your soul mate...
Your true love...!
Your happiness is mine,
and it almost overwhelms me...
O Kali, I implore you,
bless these two young people
and grant them a
long life together.
Agni!
I fear you may be making
the young lady uncomfortable.
Perhaps you could
propose at a later date?
It's almost time
for tea, miss...
You must be thirsty...
Shall we?
Today we have Nilgiri tea...
I expect you will appreciate
its refreshing aroma
and its rich flavor.
Nilgiri, eh...?
It brings back memories.
If I'm correct, Nilgiri
means "blue mountain."...
This blend fetches
an especially good price.
Accompanying the tea
is a Dundee Cake...
This treat is made from a batter
of rum and various dried fruits
studded with roast almonds.
Oh!
It looks delicious!
It isn't bad.
Thank you, my lord.
I cannot help but
notice how you're
admiring that teacup, miss.
Is that--?
Oh my!
Yes, it's a Vienna Rose...
I thought the flower on the cup
would set off the loveliness
of the young lady to advantage.
Good heavens!
It's genuine?
Yes...
Apparently it was one of Empress
Maria Theresa's favorite pieces.
A fine item, befitting
the status of an earl...
I can scarcely imagine what
it would be worth on the market.
Oh goodness!
Oh, this is no good.
Indeed...
It would be criminal to chip
cup as precious as that one.
Sebastian, see that she's
all right and prepare her
a fresh change of clothing...
The frock in the dressing
room should do nicely.
That dress, master?
Are you sure?
Yes, It's fine.
Very good.
Pardon me, miss.
If you don't mind,
I'll help you inside.
Ordinarily I would never
consider intruding upon
a young lady's
dressing routine.
However, we have no
handmaiden to help...
And this is an emergency.
I hope you can
forgive my rudeness.
There we are.
That should do nicely.
Perhaps the teacup was
too heavy for a young lady
as delicate as yourself...
I apologize for making
such a grievous blunder.
If it doesn't displease you, my
master would like you to have
this dress as a token
of our hospitality...
Please accept it
with our compliments.
Why would we go to
such lengths, you ask?
You are an honored visitor,
and the Phantomhives are famed
for taking care
of their guests.
Goodness, look at the time.
This evening's guests will
be arriving any moment now...
I must excuse myself, miss...
Would you be so kind
to wait in the guest room
with Lady Elizabeth?
Welcome to Phantomhive manor.
Sorry to barge in like this.
Why, Inspector Abberline.
What brings the Yard
to my ball, inspector?
I'm here on patrol...
There have been a number of
suspicious disappearances
at balls lately...
Disappearances?
Yes, that's right.
The cowardly scoundrel
targets only young maidens...
It's simply unforgiveable,
but you can be certain
Scotland Yard will catch him!
So you have successfully
infiltrated their ranks...
Good.
To think it only took a month
for you to gain an invitation
to Phantomhive manor.
That girl is bloody
fool for believing you
to be a respectable young lady
Well, you know your job...
Kill that damned butler
and bring Ciel Phantomhive
to me at once.
The butler uses strange
tricks, so watch out...
We will avenge Azzurro
and the Ferro family!
I suppose tonight we
shall find out just how
expert an assassin you are...
Mad Dog of Venezia.
So this is where
you disappeared to.
Forgive me, miss, but the
ball is about to begin.
Tighter...!
Make it tighter...!
Tonight is special...
I want to look my best!
I'm trying, my lady
Oh, hello my dear!
Look at my darling
new dress...!
Well...?
It's adorable... right?
Oh...!
And you...!
Ever so cute
as usuaual I see--...
That dress, uh...
It suits you so well.
You're a vision...! You have
to make certain that Ciel
sees you in it at the ball...
He'll think it looks beautiful.
My lady!
No need to be afraid.
So lovely, even in sleep.
After so long, you're mine...
I have you at last,
my darling song thrush.
Welcome to the
Phantomhive Manor.
She's vanished...
What do you mean?!
I don't know...
She's just gone!
Oh, my lady...
Escort Lady Elizabeth
to the guest room...
I'll be up shortly with a
glass of warm milk for her.
Alright.
There, there my lady...
Let's go now.
I found signs that a
sleep-inducing gas was
pumped into the room where
the ladies dewelled.
So first he put her to sleep,
and then he carried her off...
He's a bold thief to act in the
middle of a party like this.
And he managed
to give you the slip.
I apologize, my lord...
but if I may remind you,
you had ordered me
to entertain this
evening guests.
Having a guest taken from my own
manor would tarnish my name...
not to mention my reputation
as the queen's guard dog...
Your orders Sebastian...
I want the girl returned.
Yes...
my young lord.
Alone at last,
my song thrush...
You stole my heart the day
I set eyes upon you.
From our very first
meeting, I knew...
I knew that someday
you'd be mine.
What a sinful little
bird you are...
inflaming my passions
with such wild abandon.
Don't worry, dear.
No one will find us...
We're safe here on the luxury
liner I built just for you...
I call it Song Thrush's Warble.
We're free, my love...!
We can do anything...! Come,
let's run away to paradise!
You can go wherever
you'd like--alone.
The butler?
So you're our kidnapper,
Lord Druitt.
My mistress...
the goddess of beauty...
has dubbed me
Masque de Vicomte!
I'll be taking the
young lady back now,
Mr. Masque de Vicomte.
Truest love is
often forbidden...
There is only
one thing to do...
say goodbye!
Ah...
so it's poison, then?
We'll go out together,
my song thrush...
to heaven, where
nobody can follow us!
Over my deadly body, dear...
She's not on the schedule
until tomorrow you see,
so I'm afraid you
can't kill her yet.
Hello, Grell.
Why, if it isn't my Bassy...!
What a coincidence,
running in to you.
I won't let you stand
in the way of our love!
Where did he go?
We're together.
There's nothing to fear.
The bugger means to take
the woman along with him...?
Well, what a
bloody great bother.
We who have been cruelly denied
our love on Earth shall be
wed at long last in Heaven...
Like Tristan and
Isolde right before us.
Let us pass from this
world together, my love...
Soon, eternity will be ours.
I believe I already told you.
Go anywhere and you
go alone... sir.
You amaze me, as always...!
My body thrills and throbs,
fueling my fight
with passion for you!
Oh, dear...
We're falling!
Sweet song thrush...!
Never forget me!
I looove--
Servant of a goddess
or not, a fop like that
never stood a change
against the likes of us, eh?
It appears she's
finally awaking...
You're all right...
Thank goodness.
What about little
ol' me, Bassy...?
I'm so exhausted
after all that fighting.
I may faint right
where I'm standing.
Won't you hold me?
Good grief...!
I cannot believe
I had to come out here.
Will?!
Must you always mess
about before actually
getting your work
done, Setcliff?
Oooh!
How I would love
to mess about with Bassy!
We could do some very messy
things together--Wait a second!
I am working!
Here look!
Would you be kind enough
to tell me your name?
Why did you do that?
Punishment for incompetence.
This soul isn't
scheduled for death.
Eh?
Look closely at the spelling...
The two names are
one letter off.
You have the wrong person.
Oh dear...
How silly of me.
Honestly...
I tire of having such
a thick-skulled employee.
We're leaving...
If we dawdle, the soul
we're actually scheduled
to reap tonight may be
stolen away as well...
by some demon.
Do try to be careful
on your travels...
I hear the sea at night
can be dangerous.
Start paddling,
on the double!
Must you always be
such a slave driver...?
Ta-ta, Bassy, my
scrumptious noodlekins!
Shall we head back now...?
The ball awaits...
Best to keep the events of the
evening to yourself, I think?
Oh, you poor dear...!
I'm so glad you're all right.
Come...
We should let her
rest for a while.
What a terrible ordeal for
such a delicate young lady.
But she's so lovely
I can see why a man
would want to take her.
You really mustn't wake him.
He's reather quite exhausted...
While I was away, my
young master was forced
to entertain all the guests.
That's taxing enough, but
he also took great pains
to keep anyone from
learning what happened.
The excitement
has worn him out.
Sincere apologies...
my lord.
Miss...
You look confused.
Is something wrong...? Perhaps
it would clear things up if I
told you that I listened to your
entire clandestine phone call.
Such a lithe figure...
and the heavy scent
of death rises from
your skin like perfume.
But still...
I admit the Ferros chose well
hiring you as their assassin.
You played a good game...
Using innocent Lady Elizabeth to
infiltrate Phantomhive manor.
This explains your
awkwardness at tea today.
I'm glad I decided to
give you a private tour...
It enabled you to find
your way to this room...
where I can easily dispose
of you with nobody noticing.
Why, wherever do you
think you're going, miss?
Sebastian?
Have I been sleeping?
Yes indeed...
With your mouth hanging open,
I might add.
You could have
woken me up, then...
or did you want a laugh...?
Our guest...
good evening.
She's come to offer her thanks.
Oh, I see...
Well.
I'm sincerely sorry...
You suffered terribly
as a direct result
of the subpar
security at my manor.
As the head of
house Phantomhive,
I accept full responsibility
for this lapse.
If you can forgive me,
please take my hand...
You see...
the evening is young still.
The ball in your honor
has even yet to begin.
Happy Birthday!
I present to you all
today's guest of honor.
My, my what have we here?
That dress suits
you splendidly!
Look, dear...
All of these people
gathered here just for you,
to celebrate your special day!
My young master and
Lady Elizabeth have been
secretly planning
this all along...
A special surprise
party for your birthday.
Naturally, I assume the date
you gave Lady Elizabeth
wasn't your real
birthday at all.
Today has become
a celebratory day,
nonetheless...
Not only for Lady Elizabeth,
but for the entire
Phantomhive household as well.
Sebastian, here it is!
Thanks for waiting.
Oooh!
It's amazing!
I hope you like it, miss...
We were determined to prepare
you a memorable cake for you.
All right Sebastian...
It's time for you
to start singing!
Me, sing...?
Lady...
I couldn't.
It's only proper
for someone to sing
when there's
a birthday cake...!
Please, Sebastian,
do it for my friend!
I can't possibly refuse
a request from you,
Lady Elizabeth...
I shall do as you wish.
It's your birthday my dear...
Older by one more year...
This special day you turn...
May you live out your dreams!
Pardon me miss.
Your wrist must still hurt
from where I gripped it...
Let me assist you...
I'll cut off a nice little
bite for you to nibble upon,
shall I?
You must have some.
This was baked
especially for you...
Here, say...
Ahhh.
Ah, the dancing is beginning.
Goodness, look at that.
It seems you and I are the
only ones without partners.
I'd be happy to lead
you through the steps
if you would care
for instruction...
I daresay you haven't
much experience with balls.
That's right...
Stay relaxed...
Imagine the calm you feel
when you're killing someone.
You look confused again...
You want to know why
I haven't killed you...
Well, I have my duties
as a Phantomhive butler...
which include making certain
this ball goes well.
I don't care much for
the idea of sullying
my perfectly planned ball
with human blood...
and my master
ordered me to offer
you true Phantomhive
hospitality.
For the moment, at least,
that means not killing you.
Come after him at any other
time, and you will die...
But for now...
as long as you're a guest
here, I'll continue to treat
you according to my
master's wishes.
Do you understand...?
If so, give a little yelp...
Say 'woof', just like a dog.
I'm glad to hear it...
This will remain a little
secret between us then...
Agreed?
Am I a colleague
of yours, you ask?
No, miss.
I assure you I am
no professional assassin...
I am one hell of a butler...
and nothing more.
So fun...
Lovely party.
I must say, Lizzie seems
quite taken with you.
And I'm glad to have
met you today as well...
I hope you don't mind,
but that dress belonged
to my late mother...
I want you to keep it.
It should be worn.
Pardon me...
Your carriage awaits, miss.
Thank you for celebrating your
birthday here with us tonight...
I hope to see you again.
We'll always be more
than happy to offer you
the famed
Phantomhive hospitality.
For now...
I bid you goodnight.
That was quite a bother.
Apologies, my lord.
I'm bloody tired...
Bring me some tea.
Sir.