I know that the dream has died.
But why?
Hoheo taralna.
I was kind enough to save
you, and you repay me
by trying to escape.
I won't let you.
You won't be going anywhere.
Your Highness.
My threads will bind you...
forever.
You are mine.
An insect cage?
Yes...
It's for this butterfly.
With or without a cage...
I doubt it will be
going anywhere soon.
Are you talking back to me?
No.
I want more than a cage...
Flowers...! I want
it to be surrounded
by beautiful flowers...
That way it can sip up
nectar when it thirsts.
I shall see to it at once.
What is this...?
You lot are always whispering...
I wonder why that is.
They are ill-bred
and foul-tongued.
I have ordered them
to speak quietly so they
need not offend your ears, sir.
"Ill-bred and foul-tongued?"...
You wouldn't be implying
something about me, would you?
Never...
Such a thing
wouldn't occur to me.
If they whisper, I can't
know what they are saying.
And I don't like it!
From now on,
you will all speak up!
I cannot abide not
knowing what's on their minds.
Or his.
What dark thoughts
go through his head?
I'm finished.
I shall see to it.
How can I be certain that he
won't try to abandon me as well?
I should rip off his wings.
Then he would remain
by my side forever.
I have assembled all the items
you requested, Your Highness.
There are
bluebells everywhere...
It's just like...
like that other garden...
Is something wrong?
You did all this.
Yes.
Incredible...
How can you know me
so well, Claude?
Please...
Say you'll always
do such things for me.
Indeed...
I am bound to do so as long
as our contract remains.
Always a price.
This garden is nothing more
than a contractual obligation.
What is this...?
You lot are always whispering...
I wonder why that is.
If they whisper, I can't
know what they are saying.
And I don't like it!
From now on,
you will all speak up!
The master has a few
screws loose upstairs.
He's a bit of a head case.
A dim bulb, you might say.
That's enough...
There is work that
needs to be done...
Carpet the master's
chamber with red roses
to accommodate the butterfly.
The master is clearly mental.
Who needs a room full of roses?
You can do it yourself.
A proper butler delegates
the simpler tasks...
They are for lower servants.
Yes, he mustn't busy himself
with menial housework...
chores are beneath him.
Oh, really?
Beneath him, are they?
Your glasses are fogged up.
I realize you're acting
upon the master's orders,
but I think you may be
speaking a bit too loudly.
Leave us alone.
My hair grows clockwise...
Can you tell?
Mine's anticlockwise...
I go this way.
Kinda strange how much the
master fancies Claude, eh?
I don't understand the appeal.
Miss Hannah's better
looking, that's for sure...
Hello, Miss Hannah.
I see you three are
speaking this afternoon.
Yeah, the master
ordered us to.
We have no choice.
It's just wretched.
We must obey the master.
Ah...
roses?
That won't do...
Use this flower instead.
Miss Hannah's way stacked.
Some serious boobage.
I like how they jiggle.
If it wasn't for
Miss Hannah living here,
I would totally burn
down this mansion.
Burn it to ashes.
Oh, heck yeah.
In a heartbeat.
I have assembled all the items
you requested, Your Highness.
We're the ones
who assembled them.
That credit stealer.
The king of glory hogs.
There are
bluebells everywhere...
It's just like...
like that other garden...
The master was crying, huh?
Yeah, he was.
He was totally crying.
But it was kinda cute,
don't you think?
Yeah, it was a little cute.
Crying like a cute little kid.
I can hear you.
You're more irritating
than a gaggle
of gossiping fishwives
'round a fire.
Your bloody prattle
hurts my ears.
Pipe down and get to work.
I try to guide the master.
My soul speaks
to him constantly...
whispering advice.
"Master," I call...
"That isn't the right path."
"You weren't meant to
go this way."
What are you doing?
I'm making sure that the
master doesn't become lost
in the forest.
But I'm already here,
watching over him.
That's what worries me...
That he will lose himself
forever in the dark forest
known as Claude Faustus.
You should think quite
carefully before betraying him.
Do that, Claude...
and I'll kill you.
I don't fear hollow threats.
Don't forget, you're
nothing more than a sheath.
An empty hole.
Yes, just a hole
for the fellows...
Hannah...
Annafellows.
Don't make me remind you
of your place again.
Demon.
You aren't the one
who should be by his side...
Not you, Claude...
That place belongs
to someone else.
Luka Macken.
See that swing over there...?
That's where we like to play.
My brother can even
swing on it standing up
and he isn't scared
or anything.
Amazing, huh?
Those kids will all
be gone after tonight...
won't they?
Yes.
Want to know something else...?
There used to be tons
and tons of bluebells
in this garden here.
Brother and I would
put them in our hair
and pretend we were girls...
Aren't I lovely?
We had such fun,
Brother and me.
No, Claude...
You will never understand.
Such knowledge is
forever out of your reach.
A demon's only path to joy is
through the suffering of others.
Ah but these...
roses?
They won't do...
Use this flower instead.
Blue flowers to remind him
of a home forever lost.
The bluebell has a meaning
in the language of flowers.
...an eternal bond.
Did the creature die?
Life is so fleeting...
Here one moment, gone the next.
What now...?
Don't you want revenge?
Strike back at the spider
who did this to you...
Alois Trancy--the spider
who wears a human form.
Take revenge on me...
be vicious and cruel...
Tear me apart...
and live.
Such an unstable soul.
Forever wavering.
This is the cruel soul with
which the demon's sheath
is so obsessed...
He's an amusing one,
I'll grant her that.
That isn't enough
for me, however...
I require more heat...
much more.
Help me...!
Claude, where are you...?
I need you!
What's happened?
No, don't!
Why not, Master?
It'll burn you alive...!
Claude, you can't go in there!
It's all right.
The fire will take you!
Go get water.
I can't lose you!
It's all right now...
The fire is out.
We'll have the
room back shortly.
I just wanted to burn it...
the butterfly...
Set it to rest, you know.
Like a funeral...
but the fire
got out of control.
A funeral?
Everything burned...
Everything.
Set the fire.
Put out the fire.
His soul dances like a flame.
Ah, master...
I do love how
heated you can be.
I love it as well.
I don't particularly love it.
Yeah, same here.
I might...
but only a little.
Delicious.
When your soul burns red-hot,
I can almost taste it.
Incredible...
It's like nothing happened.
Come to bed, master...
It would be best for you
to get some rest my lord...
before dawn breaks.
Stay with me.
Yes, Your Highness.
You can sit on the bed.
Say...
am I entertaining?
Yes...
very.
Enough?
Enough for now.
That line again?
You're quite impertinent...
for a butler...
You never give me
a straight answer...
You're always telling me "as
long as this" or "only if that."
Why can't you say "yes"...
Would that be so difficult?
You mustn't let your fire burn
too fiercely all the time...
You shall burn yourself
right out, master...
Do take care.
I dreamt for the
first time in a long while.
There was a butterfly
caught in the spider's web...
but it had no wings.
And that butterfly...
was me.