Everyone is here, I trust?
For those who don't know, my
name is William T. Spears...
I'm your instructor...
here to mould you...
to whip you into shape.
I will be with you for the
duration of your training
as new recruits...
Should you find
something unclear,
feel free to come
to me with questions.
As my shift ends at six o'clock,
I'll answer any questions
asked before five thirty.
Now, to be--
What are you doing here?
Aren't you also
an instructor, Grell?
Oh, honey, you know
I'm not into children.
They just aren't my thing.
But you...
you I could nibble
on any day of the week.
It's been ever so long
since we were together.
Much...
too...
long.
The personnel department must've
collectively lost their minds.
You know how much I love it when
you play hard to get, Will!
Recruits...
we'll start with a tour
of the facilities.
The higher ups compile a
soul collection list so that
we grim reapers can screen those
who have been marked 'to-die'.
Using our death scythes,
we check each individual's
memories--their
Cinematic Records.
A human's Cinematic
Record contains
his entire life experience...
Based on it,
we determine whether
that person deserves death...
and if he does, it falls to us
reapers to collect his soul.
Okay, but are there really any
humans who don't deserve death?
There are some capable
of benefitting the world.
People whose continued
existence may bring about
a desirable change in the
world are sometimes removed
from the list and
allowed to live.
However, that is much more
the exception than the rule...
We merely double-check
the list to be certain
no grave mistakes are made.
We follow orders
from on high...
We don't ask questions...
or make errors.
This is the
administrative department...
They oversee the To-Die list
and the souls collected.
Personnel, in charge
of Association staff.
General Affairs, in charge
of equipment and such.
I got a table at that
French restaurant.
My shift?
Nah, I'll be done
with time to spare!
Here's Collections.
They actually harvest
the souls onsite.
And finally...
Spectacles.
Right.
Bottom.
Top-
Here they handle
all your glasses needs.
It is the backbone of the Grim
Reaper Staffing Association.
Ooh...!
My heart always goes
wobbly at this sight!
Who's the old man?
That old man is the
department head.
Lawrence Anderson.
Most call him Pops.
Him, really...?
He's the legendary
craftsman who makes
all the reapers' spectacles?
So from now on,
we'll get to wear glasses
made by the master?!
I, for one, would like a new
pair as soon as possible...
These new-recruit
models are horribly dull.
You lads are nowhere near
ready to wear Pops's glasses.
You've got a long,
long way to go yet.
In this, he's correct.
Only those who have
passed the final exam
are permitted to wear
his spectacles.
Basically...
they're a sort of proof
that you have become
a full-fledged reaper.
The final exam, sir...
what's it like?
At the end of your
training period,
you will form groups of two...
Together, you will be
tasked with screening
and collecting a soul.
You will be judged on
efficiency and accuracy...
That is the exam.
Screening and collecting?
Right out of the gate?
I don't know about you...
This year's recruits
seem a bit spineless.
If they fail, we'll just
start over with a new group.
You're every bit as cold
and cruel as ever, Will!
Just like you were
on that magical day.
What are you talking about?
Surely you remember...
I know I could
never forget it.
Yes...! Our first time
together...! What pure bliss!
I would forget it
if I could, trust me.
Ah, but the memory is
forever etched upon my body...
I tremble at the very thought!
--Honestly!
--You thrust into me
from above and from below.
Face to face and behind!
I thought for sure
my body would give out!
We have tallied the results
from the practical portion
of your exam.
Grell Sutcliff, you have a
triple A in practical skills,
a B on written exams,
and a C in ethics,
giving you an A average.
William T. Spears...
you have straight Bs
in practical skills,
written exams, and ethics,
giving you a B average.
It's obscene...
I have an A average.
How can you possibly pair me
with that B-average cretin?!
I don't recall
asking for your opinion.
In case you weren't
listening properly,
the only as you received
were in practical skills.
I rather think that's
enough, don't you...?
Practical skills are more
important than anything else...
Perhaps you'd like
a demonstration...
I can show you
my skills personally.
Don't be ridiculous.
Put that away.
You're already
on thin ice already.
You'd best not cause problems.
It won't work...
I need to be partnered
with a real man,
one who can milk me
for all I'm worth.
The human is scheduled
to die one month hence...
You both shall spend that month
working together to determine
whether or not he deserves the
death that he's slated for...
Naturally, you're free to
present your conclusion
before the month ends.
Here is the data
you'll need on the target...
We wish you good luck.
Fine...
just don't get in my way.
Right...
I shall do my utmost...
I look forward
to working with you.
The living world
is always so filthy!
I've found him.
That's our man.
That's Thomas Wallis...
Born in Bristol in 1775...
He's an aspiring novelist.
A novelist, eh...?
How dreadfully typical.
He's probably poor
and talentless,
with no love life to speak of.
Well, that's that.
This one's cleared for death.
We should use all the time
allotted to investigate.
Oh my...
Mr. B average is talking back.
How fabulous.
Well, anything else to say?
They gave us a month
to complete the exam...
This is our first screening.
I think we should
observe him further...
If we make a mistake on this,
it could ruin both our careers.
You're a dreadfully dull.
Do what you like...
but I'm telling you,
it's a waste of our time.
So...
when is the collection
scheduled for, again?
In one month,
on December 16th...
at four o'clock
in the afternoon...
We should get to work.
Observation log
of William T. Spears.
Target Thomas Wallis is an
earnest, hard-working young man.
He spends each day working at
the printer's and each night
at the boardinghouse,
writing his novels.
He's submitted
his work to publishers.
But has had no success.
He works to support
his writing,
and he submits his
manuscripts to publishers...
That seems to be
his entire life.
Hey, dullard!
What are you wearing?
Never mind my attire...
Now...
are you ready to stamp
the kid's file yet or not?
I've only been
at this for three days.
Isn't that enough...?
I'm tired of
the living world.
I haven't seen a single
attractive man here...
Hurry up and
make your decision.
All right, I will.
Good afternoon...
Don't get up...?
I am William T. Spears
at your service, sir.
Uh...
What?!
You may wish to edit this.
Your prose is
a tad roundabout.
You know it's funny,
the publisher told me
pretty much the same thing.
What the devil
are you playing at?
You told me to hurry.
That's what I'm doing.
This isn't what I meant.
Are you an idiot?!
Nothing in the test
instructions forbids us
from contacting
the target directly.
Uh...
why are you walking
around with sickles?
They're death
scythes, actually.
Quit talking!
Oh, a death scythe...
hold on, do you mean
like the Grim Reaper
carries in all the legends...?
Is that it?
Yes...
Actually, we are grim reapers.
Huh?
Yes sir...
I'm afraid you're scheduled to
die in the very near future...
So we've come to
investigate whether or not
you really ought to pass away--
I should have killed you
the first time I saw you.
Again, none of the
instructions forbid us
from identifying
ourselves to the target.
Because only an
idiot would do so!
Ah...!
I understand now.
You're actors, aren't you?
And this must be some new
form of avant-garde theatre
with audience
participation, right?
Be quiet...!
Stay out of this, boy!
You're so pretty!
You were made to be onstage!
Your flame-red hair
and porcelain skin...
I've never seen a man
so beautiful in my life!
London truly is
a city of wonders!
Oh, yes!
All the world's a stage,
and I am a player,
navigating the brutal, bloody
battlefield that is love...
Yes...!
Man and man together
in a tragic play!
Thanks to your interference,
I wasn't able to investigate.
Please, it's your fault
for talking to the boy!
I have to admit, though...
He seems a rather
promising youth.
There's something about him.
Grim reapers, eh?
The Story of Will
the Reaper continues.
Young Thomas began
a new novel.
And its title was...
...The Story of
Will the Reaper.
It was a tale of
a junior reaper and
his observations of human life.
Will watched dispassionately
as people died...
people whose souls were
neither good nor evil.
Until, one day, he fell
in love with a human maiden.
A maiden who was
destined for death.
And so, Will found himself
caught between reaper law
and the dictates
of his own heart.
In the end, love won out,
and he tried to save
his sweetheart from
her predestined death.
Will's fast friend
aided the young lovers.
"A fair skinned fellow reaper
with bright red hair...
Grell."He's a perceptive boy,
I'll give him that much.
The novel was accepted
for publication...
Thomas was given
a deadline for completion...
Four o'clock on December 16th.
That date sounds
familiar to me.
Yes...
it's the day
he's scheduled to die.
The reapers' efforts
were in vain...
The maiden died.
Will appealed to the god
who ruled that world...
He begged that the
maiden be allowed to live,
and offered his own soul
in exchange for hers.
And so it was agreed that
her life would be spared...
but there was one condition.
The maiden would have
no memory of Will.
Will could accept that.
He believed that even if all
memories of him vanished,
proof of their love would
remain in her soul.
No one could ever erase that.
And so, Will disappeared, and
the maiden was restored to life.
In time she fell
in love again...
She married and bore a child...
and she named that child...
Will.
That's not a bad little story.
No...?
It's a masterpiece.
I believe it shall be regarded
as a literary classic.
Unfortunately, the book's author
will die at four o'clock today.
The soul of a
talented novelist...
Perhaps we should
let him live...
I could contact
the association--
There is no need to do that.
We shall collect
his soul as we were told.
We shall...?
Are you forgetting
the loophole?
We're allowed to make
special exceptions for souls
that are beneficial
to the world.
"Beneficial?" ...
That boy?
You said yourself that his
novel is a masterpiece...
a literary classic!
And on the basis of my own
evaluation of his novel...
you think we should
let him live...
Is that what you're
suggesting, Grell?
Yes it is...
What of it?
Honestly.
Excuse me...
Is there a problem?
No, no problem at all...
However...
You are mistaken in this.
Oh, is that what you think...?
I am mistaken...
I am mistaken?
Those are fighting words.
Not bad.
I'd prefer not to injure you.
My grade might suffer.
Are you implying you held back
the last time we fought...?
Your B against my A...?
You don't stand a chance
in hell against me.
Having straight Bs still qualify
me to become a full reaper...
Besides...
You only received As
in a single subject.
You didn't fare so well
in the other areas.
Don't you mock me!
What--...
What's happening?
This time...
I'm on the receiving end.
From above...
From below...
Face to face...
And behind!
What is this...?
I've never known
this feeling before!
This must be love!
You may be right...
Perhaps he'll be a famous
author whose name
will go down in history...
Even so...
The world won't
notice his absence...
His life makes no difference.
It's nearly time...
We should be off now, come.
Don't...
leave...
me.
What happened?
Carriage hit 'im...
He ran right in front of it.
Pardon me.
I shall now begin the
collection of your soul.
Oi...!
What are you doing
to the poor boy?
Huh?
My glasses!
I can't work without them!
Oh no!
Blast it!
These are Thomas's memories.
They're flowing into me!
Thomas...!
Thomas!
How very rude...
First you get me all
got and bothered,
then you go off to play with
your little writer boy.
You should be more
careful with those.
Keep your hands off my man,
you dirty homewrecker...
or you'll wish you had.
I'm not your man.
Now, let's take care of this.
You may as well give up...!
Now I know why they make
new recruits work in pairs.
Ooh, tying me up are you...?
It won't do you any good...
I'm afraid you really
aren't my type at all.
This is the struggle
of a dying soul.
This is the weight of a life.
Let's send him off now, Will...?
Shall we?
Here is to the first of many
collaboration, my darling!
I am not your darling.
Looks like there are other
teams working in the area.
My such a cold, cruel beauty.
How very fetching.
Congratulations.
You're officially full members
of the Grim Reaper
Association...
Now, go off and get yourselves
some proper spectacles.
At last, ravishing
reaper Grell emerges.
A deadly star is born!
Only those who have known
and measured the weight
of a life are given
true reaper glasses.
Glasses of life.
Honestly.
Being saved one time by
you is the only blot
on my otherwise spotless
life's record.
Huh...?
Did you say something?
The final sounds
really difficult.
You have to sit there
and watch a human die.
Seems pretty rough to me.
Remember, it's just a job.
And there is no place
for emotion in a job...
We do our duty as grim reapers,
no more, no less...
We follow the orders
that come from on high.
We don't ask questions.
Or make errors.
How utterly delectable.
Oh, one more thing...
Be careful with your glasses.