I can hear water running.
Light hits my eyelids...
I can feel it...
summer sunshine.
Where is this...?
Am I dreaming it?
The reflection
you see is no dream...
It's the next chapter...
A golden afternoon.
And if I opened my eyes...?
What would I see
when I woke up?
It's time, my lord...
Open your eyes.
Sebastian...
You were sleeping very soundly.
Well, master...
we have very nearly arrived.
Now there is work to be done.
This area has been plagued
by floods for many years...
It is my hope that the addition
of new floodgates will restore
Phantomhive lands
to peace and safety...
Additionally...
I would like to thank all of
you for your continued support
in this grand endeavor.
I shall commit myself to
the task of flood prevention,
as my family has for
generations before me
in the hope of bettering
all our lives.
If you ask me, the earl's
speech was positively shameless.
Oh yes, And from what
I've been hearing,
that company of his
is making more money
than he knows
what to do with...
They're saying that...
That much...!
How indecent!
I certainly hope the child
doesn't allow his vanity
to get him into
too much trouble.
I'd wager there is a man or two
who might wish differently
for the young lord.
Do tell.
Who might that be?
I would appreciate
any wisdom you can offer
from your vast experience.
Oh, not at all.
I'm sure there's nothing
we three could possibly
hope to teach you!
Er... Heavens no!
And... by the way, my lord...
I recently caught wind
of a grand opportunity...
If you will...
Pardon us...
I'm afraid my master
has another engagement.
What tiresome people.
Ciel!
Elizabeth!
I'm so very excited...!
Look at this, Ciel!
Whatever it is,
I can't see like this.
It's a deer.
A deer?
There's an elusive deer
living on a hill near here...
It's ever so rare!
Oh is it now.
A cute white stag
that makes people happy!
I've never heard of
such a thing.
There is a legend.
The elusive white stag of which
you speak is traditionally
considered a messenger
of the netherworld...
Those who receive his
message are supposedly
blessed with good
fortune and happiness.
Exactly...!
You know everything don't you!
Why thank you, my lady.
It nothing but
a stupid fairy tale.
No, I know it's true...!
There are witnesses
and everything!
Please, Ciel...!
Let's go and look for it!
Not today...
I'm too busy for this.
Not fair!
Elizabeth, please!
I say. It's terrible manners
to make your fiancée cry.
So do you think they're engaged
or only playing 'house'?
This could mean my
youngest niece still has
a chance with the earl.
Sebastian...
prepare a boat to sail.
Of course.
Lady Elizabeth.
There is another
floodgate downstream
that I'd like to inspect...
Perhaps you would favor me
with your gracious company?
I am told that
a legendary white stag lives
in this part of the country...
Have you heard tell of it?
Yes...
I have!
I'd like to come
with you very much.
Have you decided
upon one, my lady?
A simplistic style would be
best for boating...
but that one's just adorable...!
And I do love those frills...!
It's not fair...!
I don't want to choose!
I wish I could
wear both at once!
Please, lady, take all the
time you'd like to decide.
Yes miss!
I thought you'd planned
to head home, master.
Plans do change.
What this is my duty,
and I will see to it.
Managing the river...
participating in
dull socializing...
and keeping my
betrothed happy...
It is all my duty as the
head of house Phantomhive.
Besides which...
I can't let those nobles
underestimate me.
I'll go see to
the boat, master.
Oh...!
Lovely!
Oi, Sebastian...
how come they're all
gawking over there...?
It's not a bloody circus.
They're trying to find fault
with our young master...
He does have impressive number
of social enemies.
Enemies?
Dear! But why?
Many are looking for
personal gain...
For instance, if the lord's
engagement should break off...
Not a break-up?!
Now...
all of you behave yourselves.
Try not to come up with
any crackpot schemes.
Yes sir!
They mustn't break up!
Lady Elizabeth's the
only one for the master!
So we've got to help him
hold on to her!
Right...
let's take care of it...
We'll do anything
we can, agreed?
Hip, hip, hurrah!
Look...!
I saw something over there!
Here we go!
Yes, sir!
Drat...!
I was certain the stag
was somewhere over in
this direction.
I found a stag!
Look, I got 'im, uh-huh!
Here we go!
Surely you're joking.
Those look like
deer to you lot?
Enjoy your brief peace, Ciel...
for, it is a transient
thing that, once lost,
one can never hope to regain.
Ciel Phantomhive...
Your die has been cast.
So...
where will you place your bet?
The current odds:...
six to one Lady Elizabeth
will find what she seeks;
four to one the
search will fail.
Place your bets,
ladies and gentlemen!
You heard him.
Bet on the long odds.
Step up and take a risk.
It's one-oh-eight to one
on the engagement ending.
So come right on up here
and place your bets!
What is he doing...?
Idiot.
And I had so hoped we'd be able
to find the stag by lunchtime.
If it wasn't hard to find, it
wouldn't be elusive, would it?
Yes.
I suppose you're
right about that...
Well...
we'll just have to eat lunch
and then go back to searching.
What do we have on
the menu today, Sebastian?
We have a delightful picnic
luncheon prepared...
There will be a shrimp salad
as well as a salmon pie...
and Cheshire cheese sandwiches
to round out the meal.
Say...
did anybody else hear
a strange noise?
Sincere apologies...
There seems to have been
an ever so slight mistake.
What is it, Sebastian...
That isn't like you.
Honestly...!
What blasted game
are you playing?
One moment more
please, my lord.
Things become even more
interesting when the butler
makes an unprecedented mistake.
Will their engagement be broken?
Will their passion fade?
Odds are sixty-to-one.
Place your bets now!
First off, the ingredients
have to be fresh...!
Catch it, trim it,
and eat it...
A premade pie is inexcusable.
And the pigeons I caught, we'll
be able to use them too, right?
Oh, we will...!
We just lightly roast
them with this beauty,
and the little lady's
sure to be all smiles!
Sebas--
--tian!
That hurt!
Good gracious...
How many times
must I remind you?
I specifically said...
...that you were to behave.
Do I make myself clear?!
Oi...
downright impressive...
As ever.
If I couldn't make a simple
dish such as this...
well, then what kind
of butler would I be?
May I present fish and lobster
soufflé with roast pigeon
in the style of the Pyrenees.
It's so lovely...!
One moment though.
Isn't this different than
the menu you listed before?
I made some alterations to
showcase the local ingredients,
my lady.
It looks so cute!
Indeed...!
Well done...!
Quite a feast...!
Cheers...!
Any young lady
would be delighted!
Step on up and place those
bets before it's too late.
A parfait with
fresh raspberries.
It's delicious!
The cream came straight
from a Jersey cow, my lady...
Thus it possesses a simple,
yet incomparably light taste.
I expect a lot from you,
but I never would have thought:
dairy farmer...
The image alone is enough
to make me smile.
Quite so, lord...
It is rather unusual...
There are few masters who
would ask their butler
to do such a thing.
Aww...!
The two of you make
simply adorable friends!
Wha...?!
He is not my frie--
The stag is nowhere
to be found...!
How positively bothersome!
Turn back?
No! Not yet!
All right.
It's peaceful...
serene...
quiet...
So why am I unsettled?
What's the matter Ciel?
Nothing at all, lady.
Are you certain?
A bit further...
We'll find it!
The clouds grow
heavy with rain.
The skies part...
It looks as though Lady
Elizabeth will not find
what she seeks here today...
The betrothal seems
uncertain indeed...
Our current odds are...
Well, Ran-Mao,
Aren't you bold today...
You really believe they'll find
the mythical stag, do you...?
Ah, well.
I do love an exciting game.
Elizabeth...
You really ought to wait.
I just saw it!
Over there in the woods.
Even the stag
will seek shelter...
Let's go back.
No...!
I'm going to find it, Ciel!
Aren't you being
a bit unreasonable...?
We can look for it
whenever we like.
Better yet, we can hire people
and offer a reward...
But for now...
Do you know...
you're a complete...
A complete idiot!!
That's what you truly think?
What does it matter
what I think...?
You wouldn't understand what I'm
feeling anyway...! Never mind!
Elizabeth!
Aww...
You've gone and
made the Lady angry.
Does this mean it's over?
Lau!
And here I bet on you
finding that white stag...
Do you insist on
disappointing me?
Why should I care about you?
"A true gentleman is charged
with pleasing his lady,"...
yes?
Being an English nobleman
must be such a bother.
I was born one.
It doesn't bother me
in the least.
But still...
my past...
I was born into
a disgraced family...
I have a duty.
All right, then...!
I've collected all my money.
We'll be going now.
We're headed after
Elizabeth, Sebastian.
Sebastian!
Yes, what is it now?
Lady Elizabeth's in trouble.
We have to help her!
Lady Elizabeth!
'old on tight, me lady!
No...!
You can't do that...!
Pull too hard and she'll
capsize, yes she will!
Elizabeth!
You came for me!
I saw the stag...
on the other side o--
Careful...!
Please, just don't let go!
I'm going to find it...
I am!
I'll find the stag.
Oh, Elizabeth...
why must you?
Whatever I have to do,
you will find happiness!
Master...
what shall we do?
She won't last long
like that...
Just look there.
An old-fashioned floodgate...
One my Master had
fully intended to begin
rebuilding next month.
It's sprung a leak...
When it bursts, the water
it's barely holding back now
will flow upstream, and this
whole area will be washed away.
Sebastian.
This is an order.
Stop it from flooding!
And Lady Elizabeth?
What would you have
me do about her?
Do I need to repeat myself...?
I'll protect Elizabeth.
That is my duty to do.
Yes...
my young lord.
Sebastian, what are you doing?!
I will protect you...
No matter what.
I have you!
Master.
It's good to see that
your with us...
my lord.
Ciel!
I'm sorry!
I'm so, so sorry!
Hurrah!
I shouldn't have done that!
Please look at me.
I'm glad you're all right.
And you as well...
I'm glad you're alright.
Sebastian...!
Why in the hell did
you open the gate...?!
I ordered you to stop
the flood, didn't I?
Yes you did...
and I followed your order.
Are you joking?
I doubt we need to worry
about a flood here now...
Or in the future.
In order to restore the
proper flow of the river,...
the dammed-up water
had to be released.
I guided the current
as necessary with
a bit of help
from the others...
Together we were able
to alter the river's course...
We showed it its way...
its rightful form.
"Rightful form?"
Yes...
How it flowed thousands
of years ago...
when the white stags
could still be found here.
Really...?
But we didn't find
a stag, did we?
Don't worry...
I'm sure we'll find it someday.
If you're still
looking for it...
It's right over there.
Is that really it?
A white stag!
It's a hill figure.
Yeah, whas' that then?
An ancient geoglyph cut into
the chalky rock of a hill...
The torrent earlier washed away
the surface of that hill...
revealing the art
hidden underneath.
This is the actuality
behind the legend.
It's amazing, Sebastian!
If I couldn't find
the legendary stag...
what kind of butler would I--
"The river does not change...
and yet you cannot step
in the same river twice,
for it is always flowing.
So it is with the
dwellings of man."
Tanaka!
It's been so long!
Where were you?
D-Don't tell me--
You were in there?!
With no one tending it,
the glyph became unimportant...
It withered and was eventually
forgotten as the years passed.
But now...
we've found it...
There it is...
back again...
How can I ever thank you, Ciel?
Why me...?
You were the one who
was looking for it.
One more thing...
Tell me...
was it fun?
I had fun...
It was a bit scary...
but it was a great day...
because I spent it with you.
It's just...
well, your work...
You're always running
off to do something
or other for her majesty...
and then...
when you come back
you always look so upset...
and that's why...
They say that people
who see white stag
are granted happiness for
the rest of their lives.
I want that for you.
Lizzie...
At last, you called me that!
I want you to
remember this sight...
for the rest of your life.
Thank you...
Lizzie.
Congratulations...!
Oh Congratulations...!
Yes Congratulations!
And thank you!
Not this again.
Indeed...
That's not all...
Invitations and interviews,
my young lord...
You're quite popular...
It appears that the social
crowd can't seem to get
enough of you since
your day at the river.
What a bother.
It is a regrettable
necessity that you treat
these people well and
build connections, sir.
It'll be a novel experience
for our private customers...
You could parley this
opportunity to expand into
the travel business
if you like.
Whatever.
rightful form eh...
Yes.
I believe I just spotted
a flash of red...
Ugh...
I have this hideous foreboding.
Ah...
You have not seen this
before, young master?
If you should find yourself
cornered, never fear...
Simply maintain eye contact,
back away, and call out
"Oh dear, have you
gained weight?"
Next time: "Wench Butler"
If I couldn't provide an
accurate image for my master,
what kind of butler would I be?