Our story so far:
While chasing after
the White Rabbit,
young Alice tumbled
into Wonderland...
There, she...
Was nearly drowned
in a sea of tears...
Was spun relentlessly
'round by the Mock Turtle...
Was brutally forced
to choke down a curry bun...
And shamelessly
erected her Eiffel Tower.
After this series of incidents,
poor Alice was growing
quite tired of Wonderland...
but if anything,
her trials were about
to become even more grueling.
Oh party train.
Damn and blast...
Where did that
White Rabbit get to?
And why the devil have
I shrunk to this size?
Ah...
so you have finally
located my hideaway.
Who are you?
I'm the Caterpillar,
of course...
I suspected this day
would come sooner or later.
I've waited for it
most eagerly.
Been waiting, have you...?
In that case, maybe you can tell
me what my next move should be.
I'm afraid I've no idea
what you're asking.
Quit dithering and
give me an answer!
The right side will
make you grow taller
and the left will
make you grow shorter.
Here in Wonderland,
that's just how things work.
More nonsense prattle!
The fungi.
The fungi?
One moment...!
What are you doing?
Suck here.
I beg your--
My...!
look at you, all grown up,!
Enough games...!
You will restore me
to normal!
I can't see why you would
want me to do that...
There are ever so many
pleasures only an adult
can properly enjoy.
Surely you don't want
to miss out on those.
Do as I say right now!
The fungi.
Can't we go about this
in a less intimate way?
Don't be such a killjoy...
Just relax and savor
the moment while it lasts.
Suck again.
This isn't right either!
Well...
That particular form comes with
its own unique pleasures also...
Why must you be so choosy?
Put me back at once...!
Or I will destroy you!
Yes...
fine, all right.
The Valley.
I'm no better off now that
I was before all this.
By the by, I was
wondering, Miss--
Oh, terribly sorry...
I don't know your name.
You didn't bother
to ask it until now.
Well, how could I with all
your babbling about becoming
larger and smaller and
then larger again...?
And what good
would it have done...?
You yourself hardly seem
to know who you are anymore.
I do know...!
I am Ciel, Earl Phantomhive!
Oh...
so is that what you think...?
That doesn't seem
to fit, somehow.
Well, it's true...
Now tell me where
the White Rabbit is.
Oh!
Why didn't you say that's what
you wanted in the first place?!
You know?
Tell me!
I haven't the foggiest.
Quit toying with me!
This was a
colossal waste of time.
Nothing but a useless
conversation with a useless bug!
You think I'm useless, eh...?
I wouldn't say
that if I were you.
What good have you done me?
Have you forgotten that
I am the Caterpillar...?
My life is a whole series
of transformations...
First, I become a chrysalis...
and, following that change...
You know what happens...
don't you?
You become...
a butterfly?
You can come along
for the ride, Alice...
It's time to spread those
wings, don't you think?
Now!
What the--?
The more that you hurry,
the later you will become...
and the more closely you look,
the less you shall find.
Young Alice can race about
on her White Rabbit hunt,
but I doubt their
paths will ever cross.
No use wondering why the
mushroom sprouted wings...
At any rate, Alice was
traveling once again,
moving swiftly
through the sky.
Quite a fast woman, our Alice.
Would it have been too much
trouble to let me down
a bit nearer the ground?
Mr. Rabbit...!
Oh, Mr. Rabbit...!
Wherever are you, Mr. Rabbit?
Meow...
I insist upon
seeing all of you!
Come on.
I shan't converse
with half a creature!
Ah, but I am a creature
of halves and in-betweens...
Am I male or female?
Naughty or nice?
No one can say...
And so I dwell here
in the shadows.
Enough of your gibberish...!
Show yourself.
Is something troubling you?
Depending on the circumstances,
I might be willing to lend
a hand.
I'm sure you will be just as
useless as everybody else
I've met in this
wretched place.
Must you be so cruel...?! I've
come to show you the way,
and this is how you treat me?
You're here to help
guide me, are you...?
Ok,which way do I go?
Well...?
Which do I pick?
I myself would be rather
inclined to take both of them.
Two...
at...
a...
time...!
I couldn't possibly narrow
it down to just one!
I mean...
Both are delicious.
I'd love to sink
my teeth into them!
I was not asking about
your taste in men, you loon...
I just want to know which
of these two paths
I ought to take, alright!
Being loved is the
easiest path, of course...
yet I always choose
to be the lover.
I am but a poor, lost kitten.
Such is my fate.
First you say you're here
to show me the way,
then you tell me you're lost?
Love is a labyrinth
with many twists and turns.
How shall I
navigate this maze...
when I have lost my thread?
I suppose I don't much
care where I end up,
so long as it is some
place other than here.
It doesn't really matter
which path you choose.
Either way you go, you will only
find a madman waiting for you...
So take your pick.
I'm absolutely mad about both
of them...! Mad, mad, mad!
There is another option...
I could simply refuse
to choose either path.
Dear me...
Can you really afford
such indecision...?
That could be dangerous.
It's...
showtime!
Oh...!
How thrilling...!
Are you ready for this?
The threesome of
paths forms a Y...
Y!
Until the tangled
limbs become an M...
M!
When only one rod's left,
it becomes...
an I!
This cat loves to dance...
Wouldn't you like to watch?
Seems as if we can put to bed
all those annoying fears
of being lost,
wouldn't you say?
So my choice of paths has
dwindled down to one.
You're dead right about that!
And now I must continue
my hunt for true love...
My claws are itching
for a fresh catch.
And as there's no suitable
prey hereabouts...
Please do give the
White Rabbit my best.
Ta-ta! Meow!
Wait, come back here a moment.
What... now?
You mentioned something
about the White Rabbit...
So, do you know
where he's got off to?
Oh, I see.
Desperately longing
for him, are you?
I...
no...
That isn't what I said.
Just how badly do
you want to see him?
Well, I...
I'm curious.
Of all the creatures
in Wonderland,
why are you seeking
the White Rabbit?
Why...?
I'm after him because
he's my butler...!
As such, he belongs to me.
I merely want my
servant back, that's all.
That's not fair...!
I want him, too, you know...
I am one of his beloved
pussy cats, after all.
Meow!
Feel free to
vanish again now.
Of course, if he prefers,
I'll play the role of tomcat,
and he can be the pussy...!
I'll do anything
for my darling!
Bloody poof,
sod off already!
More indecision...! You're
the one who told me to wait!
That's correct, I did, and you
never answered my question.
Where can I find
the White Rabbit?
Never fear, Alice I've no
doubt you'll be seeing him
straight away...
Well, straight that way...
Simply keep heading
straight and then straight
and then straight some more...
You shall find
him eventually...
or perhaps you shan't.
I really must be going though.
Ta-ta!
The White Rabbit is
straight that way, he says...
Huh.
The Cheshire Cat
never much cared
for playing the
role of guide...
His interests lay elsewhere...
Indeed, he was a whore...
for attention, I mean.
With only one road
to choose from,
poor Alice was forced
to trudge forward.
Ciel...
in Wonderland.
Ciel in Wonderland.
There is no more room.
Yes, no more room at all.
Come, don't say that.
Have a seat.
I haven't said anything yet...!
What do you mean?
The Dormouse was talking
in his sleep again...
That's where
his name comes from...
always speaking endormi.
Greetings, and welcome
to the Mad Tea Party...
If you haven't guessed,
I am the Hatter.
And my companion
is the March Hare.
Now, may I offer you
a cup of tea?
I...
er...
I discern a suspicious
look in your eye...
There's nothing in it,
I assure you.
Nothing but a cube
or two of tasty sugar.
You can stop...
That's quite enough sugar.
Shhh...
Take a look at the cup.
What on Earth?
Memories are such
ephemeral things,
fading as quickly
as they appear.
Enough of your parlor tricks.
Oh...
my, my...
See how quickly the tea
is disappearing?
The ground is thirsty.
I don't want tea.
I want to know if you've
seen the White Rabbit.
An interesting question,
but I'm sure I don't remember.
And what about your guest over
there in the spectacles, eh...?
He's a rabbit
as well isn't he?
I'll thank you kindly
not to lump me in
with that disgusting beast!
Come now, a rabbit
is a rabbit...
Those ears suit you,
by the way.
I happen to be a hare,
you ignorant wretch...!
That white creature is
nothing but a common rabbit!
Oh...
All right,
all right, all right.
Gracious...!
Are all children as poorly
educated as you these days?
Rabbit or hare, what's the
bloody difference, anyway?
How many times must
I explain this to you?!
Enough of that.
On to more important question.
Tell me, why is a raven
like a writing desk?
Eh?
If you want to find the rabbit,
you have to pay the price...!
Now then...
You'd best start thinking.
You have a question
to answer, you know.
The quiz is now beginning...
The rules are simple.
When you know the answer, be
the first one to ring the bell.
All right...
Your first question: why is a
raven like a writing desk...?
You'll be given
two hours to answer.
That's long!
Ready?
Your time to think begins now.
You have thirty
seconds to go...
29, 28, 27--
I say!
Pardon, March Hare, I was
under the impression that
your watch was broken.
Weren't you going to
take it in for repair?
14, 13, 12, 11, 10, 9, 8, 7, 6--
Hey!
The first one to
answer is Alice!
Both sound like they
start with an "r"
Da-dum-da-dum-da-duuum.
The right answer...
is that they are not
alike... at all.
Right answer, my arse...!
That wasn't at all a proper
quiz question, you fool!
I beg to differ.
Indeed, you are the fool
for expecting everything
to have a clear answer.
Quite right...
real life isn't
nearly so sweet.
That's why we all crave a bit of
sugar to sweeten things up.
I told you, I don't care
for your tricks...!
I'm through with
this den of lunatics...!
Good day!
Have you been to visit
the Queen's castle?
No, I haven't yet.
In that case, allow me
to give you a warning...
You'd be better off staying
well away from the queen...
She is capricious,
selfish, and savage.
One can never know what
punishment she will dish out
at the slightest provocation.
It could be quite nasty.
Even so, she is
still worth meeting...
She holds the highest office
around here, doesn't she?
Well, yes, I suppose so.
I can't think of anyone higher.
Oh dear...
I know that sound.
What is it?
It seems they've come for you.
For Alice.
We present an invitation
from the Queen.
Yes, from the Queen, we present
an invitation for Alice.
An invitation from the Queen for
Alice we present to you today.
Right, then...
Let's go!
Hip, hip, hurrah...!
Put me down this instant!
I can walk on my own,
thank you!
Company...
halt!
So sorry, Alice.
Are you all right?
I'll be fine once I know where
the damn White Rabbit is?
Ah...
He was headed for
the castle, I think.
He runs away from me every
time I catch sight of him...
Well, he shan't be getting
anywhere this time...
You three shall escort me
to the castle immediately!
Yes, my young mistress.
If Wonderland were a chessboard,
the Queen's castle would be
on the eighth rank...
Whether Alice was the defender
or the attacker remained
an open question,
but, regardless,
her adventure was
nearing its end.
This place is strange.
I can't begin to guess
why I was called here.
Presenting Her Majesty,
the Queen of Hearts...
the most beneficent
of rulers...
sovereign among sovereigns...
leader of all creatures
great and small!
Guardian of law and
administrator of justice!
And, um, er...
Provider of delicious stews and
overseer of rubbish pick-up...
All bow before
Her Glorious Majesty...
Theeee...
Queeeeeen!
Silence.
The trial will now commence...
Hear my ruling...
The accused, Alice,
is sentenced to death.
We will have order
in the court...!
Silence, everybody!
Off with her head!
Off with it immediately, I say!
Off with my what?!
Do you know, I have always
wanted to say that...
Why are you standing there?
I gave you an order, didn't I?
Uh-uh-uh-uh...
Yes, of course,
Your Majesty.
Stuff and nonsense!
I object to this fast!
You pass the sentence
first, with no accusation
and without
presenting evidence?!
Naturally.
Going through all of that
business is a waste of time,
and it's so dreadfully boring.
You can't behead me
because you're bored.
That's insanity!
Very well, if we must...
Go on and read the accusation,
then, just for form's sake.
Yes, Your Majesty.
For form's sake, Your Majesty!
Quite right.
It isn't for form's sake,
it's for justice!
Er, well...
all right...
At any rate, here we are...
"The accused, Alice, was born
on 14th December, 1875...
"And, let's see here...
Yes...
I do believe that's everything.
I object...!
What's my birthday got
to do with anything?!
Are you suggesting
my birth was a crime?!
You will be silent...
Or I shall hold you in contempt
and have you chucked out!
We-we will now call the first
witness to the stand...
Witness, you are ordered,
please, to approach the stand.
Yes.
Now, uh, miss, I believe
you have been wronged
by the accused.
Please tell your story.
It's awful...
so awful...
I lost all of
my pretty colors...
I wanted to wear
a pink hat today...
with this darling flower on it.
But I couldn't, you see, because
a widow may only wear black,
day after day.
Which is because of her!
Because of me...?
That's mad!
Would the second witness please
approach the stand now?
I tragically lost
the love of my life!
The very woman I had adored
since I was but a boy!
At the time, he gained
a friend in exchange,
but now he has been
lost as well!
Which is because of her!
Apologize now, I'll forgive you.
Apologize for what?
I lost all the days
that could have been.
Still...
be that as it may...
I won't say it was
because of you, Alice.
Whether you say it or not,
the truth will remain the truth.
I lost my wings and
the power to fly!
Which is because of Alice.
And...
We finally found a warm,
comfortable place to call home!
We tried, but in spite of
all we did to protect it,
we have lost it once again.
Which is because of Alice.
It is my sincere honor to call
the next witness, Her Majesty.
Very well...
I lost my life...
and, perhaps, something even
more important than that...
I lost my sanity.
See, Alice...
every last bit of this
was your fault...
How cruel of you to make
so many people unhappy.
I don't recall that.
Oooh...
You still have the gall
to claim innocence...
Even following all the evidence
you've seen in court today?
I have no memory of any of it.
Indeed...
Loss of memory
is your crime, Alice.
My crime...? But how?
Now...
will the final
witness come forth?
Don't you remember
what I told you...?
Memories are such
ephemeral things, Alice.
You have entered
a dreamland...
a realm between
life and death...
a place where past and future
meet and blend together.
I don't...
remember.
To come here,
you have to travel light.
Your memories were left
behind in the human world...
And now here you are,
a shell of yourself...
Poor lost Alice.
Am I Alice...?
The name seems wrong,
like a shoe that doesn't fit.
Very interesting...
Nice analogy.
Alice isn't right...
But I can't remember what
my name might actually be.
I told the Caterpillar
when he asked,
but now I can't think of it.
Thus proving my
judgment correct.
As ruled by her Majesty, the
Queen, the accused is hereby
found guilty on the charge
of losing her memories.
Her sentence will be...
It's death, of course...
Now...
off with her head before
I am bored to death.
You can't.
I'm innocent, I tell you!
Are you...?
Show your proof.
Show your proof!
I don't know what
I'm supposed to do!
Show your proof.
Proof that whatever else
you may forget...
you will remain yourself.
Now...
simply call my name.
Sebastian...
Call it louder.
Sebastian, Sebastian,
Sebastian, Sebastian!
Listen to me now,
Sebastian...!
It doesn't matter if I lose
everything, I am still me!
I am always
Ciel Phantomhive...!
Now come to me, Sebastian!
Master!
That was well done
indeed, my lord.
I order you...
get me out of
here immediately!
Immediately...
yes my young lord.
Seize them quickly!
Hold on tightly.
So you're going home...
at last...
Let us meet again, Ciel.
In another dream.
The truth is, you never need
any proof at all...
You have only to evoke me
and give me my orders.
Simply call my name...
and I shall come.
"'Who cares for you'?
said Alice.
'You're nothing but
a pack of cards'...
At this, the whole pack
rose up into the air
and came flying down upon her."
She gave a little
scream of fright..."
And then...
she found herself lying in bed,
safe and sound in her own world.
It ends there.
Sweet dreams, young master.