And now, master...
What is this?
Group attack...
Welcome to...
The Fierce Raking from Hell!
Good show.
You're all
exceptionally skilled.
It was like carrying a doll...
Running virtually unburdened.
Did you say something?
Only that it would be far,
far easier to carry you
if you were in a container.
Like a trunk, I'd say.
Is this any time to be joking?
My apologies, master.
Sebastian's amazing...
You know, Claude, I think
he may be better than you.
We should force him to crawl
on his belly like a dog.
What do you think?
Can you make
that happen, Claude?
What's that?
What's in there?
An instrument, maybe?
This is a surprise...
I certainly didn't expect
to see that here tonight.
See what?
You know what that is?
My prince!
Wh-
What's happening?
Master, please cover your ears.
My ears?
Why?
What is that noise?!
I haven't heard it in awhile...
At least a hundred
years, I believe.
My lady!
It hurts my head!
I didn't drink that much.
I say...
what is this?
If you know something...!
Know what?
You damn crook!
Prince Soma!
Has everyone gone mad?
It is the music...
It seems to be
controlling them somehow.
Let's go...!
We need to get
back to the ball.
Don't worry, master...
Fortunately, one of my very few
friends is at the dance evening.
Oww-ee!
Oh, it's all quiet now!
That music doesn't
hurt me head anymore!
Knew I didn't have
that much to drink...
Hey!
Why do we sound all funny?
Our lines don't fit the flaps!
Almost like
someone else's talking!
On your guard.
Here they come.
I am sorry.
Agni, stop this...!
Knock them all unconscious.
Jo ajna!
Master, are you all right?
Fine.
Just shut your mouth and run.
Right.
Damn...
there are too many!
Prince Soma!
...Your Highness!
Are you alright, my Prince?
Yes, Agni...
but what is happening?
The sound has changed.
Look, it's Sebastian!
I feel all
peaceful-like somehow.
It's very relaxing!
This is magnificent.
Sebastian's music is merging
perfectly with hers,
transforming the
quality of the sound...
Her threatening, ominous
playing becomes a melody full
of warmth and kindness...
Such a complete change
is incredible.
We are blessed to be able
to witness such purity
in a performer...
True beauty,
utter transcendence,
thank you Sebastian!
He plays like
some sort of god!
The Earl certainly
knows how to entertain.
Bravo!
I still don't
understand what happened.
The performance
would not have been
the same without your help...
I'm grateful, my lady.
Hmph...
What a show off.
You're back, Ciel.
What is the instrument
she was playing?
An armonica...
It was popular
in the eighteenth century.
Some called it the "voice
of the angels." Others feared
that it disturbed the minds
of those who heard it.
Thus it fell into the
dark corners of history
as a demon's instrument.
Made by humans and called
a demon's instrument.
Yet its negative effects
didn't seem to reach you.
Yes...
I found it rather pleasant.
Why would someone play such
a thing at a costume ball?
As a diversion for my guests.
Ladies and gentlemen, please
accept my sincere apologies
for being late.
I'm Alois Trancy,
I'm so honored that you came.
Oh, so that's him!
He's young!
I see that you enjoyed the
entertainment while I was away.
I'm relieved that
it was to your liking.
That performance
was outstanding...
I must say, you have a true
talent for music, Sebastian.
I cannot accept such praise...
I am simply one hell
of a butler.
Yes, he is quite a servant...
You're lucky,
Earl Phantomhive.
He's merely a butler.
Master...
I'd like to have
a word with Claude if
it wouldn't trouble you.
It shouldn't
take terribly long.
He can do that...
Right, Claude?
Ten minutes, Claude...
I want you to settle
this quickly...
If you can't do that...
you'll be punished.
Yes...
your highness.
Fine, but do it swiftly...
Understood?
Why, yes...
my young lord.
You're nothing
if not persistent...
You've been hunting
my master most relentlessly.
My master ordered it...
He instructed me to
"steal Ciel Phantomhive
from Sebastian Michaelis."
Nevertheless,
he is my young master.
Just the feel of him...
One rarely handles
something so fine.
I cannot abide the thought that
someone else has touched him...
It's enough to make me sick.
The sticky, clinging touch
of your vile spider web
has defiled him...
My master.
Ciel Phantomhive.
...his soul.
What is this?
This is impossible...
My lord is empty.
That was the day you took him
from me, you underhanded thief.
You stole my precious
young master's soul.
It wasn't enough, though.
I needed more than the soul;
I needed the body, as well.
But then you came here.
Yes, I retrieved
his soul from you.
And yet, something
was not right,
he was still not
my young master.
Now...
young master
It is time to wake up.
Ciel Phantomhive
lost his memories.
He lost the pain
he had lived through.
My lord's soul, which I'd
so carefully cultivated.
As I thought.
You want a soul
that's known its revenge.
Even so...
I sense an extraordinary
attachment to him...
A fierce obsession
with the boy's soul.
Not surprising...
I am a demon after all...
You have a master of
your own, you should know.
Nurture a soul
and then feast upon it.
That is what we do.
Yes, I do know...
My master's soul is another of
the rare ones worth desiring.
But you...
Giving a soul
that's lost its memory...
A second chance at revenge...
No human soul is
worth the trouble.
That's where
you're wrong, I'm afraid.
My master is unlike any
human you've known...
He's a very rare specimen.
You were right about
one thing, though...
I most definitely intend to
give him a second opportunity
to realize his vengeance...
But sadly...
I'm lacking something critical.
A worthy target.
What are your master's orders?
You said they were
to steal my master from me.
Is that all?
That and to make you suffer
an agony worse than death.
Is that so?
It would be pointless to obtain
Ciel Phantomhive without
his memories of
revenge fully intact.
I must steal a perfected version
of him, one who has known
his final vengeance.
Would you be
interested in a deal?
How is it, Ciel?
Does it bring
back any memories?
And what, exactly,
is eating bread stuffed
with curry supposed
to make me remember...?
Besides, I don't even
care for spicy foods anyway.
I'm sorry, my prince.
Although...
You know, the flavor
isn't all that bad.
--What are you doing?
--Hello, Lord Phantomhive...
So, how did everything
turn out in the end?
Wait, you've just been
hiding under the table?
You and your master shall
become the targets
of my lord's revenge.
And once Ciel Phantomhive
has gained that revenge,
we shall battle for his soul...
The seal.
We make our pact.
One minute...
That's all.
You're back, Claude!
What's the meaning of this?
I took care of it swiftly, just
as you ordered me to, my lord.
Quit playing games!
What is this?
This looks as if they've
been investigating me?
And my father as well...?
Then that means...
He is the one.
It's him!
Care to explain why
Sebastian's still alive?
You botched this...
How sad.
You failed me.
What shall I do...?
I'll have to punish you now.
Your Highness, you did not order
me to kill Sebastian Michaelis.
All the arrangements
have been made...
Day into night...
snow-white into crimson...
lies into truth.
Indeed...
I am a Trancy butler.
I will make one hell
of a feast out of you.
Ciel...!
Where are you? Ciel?
Lady Elizabeth...
So, shall we dance?
Oh, hello my lord.
Forgive me for
bumping into you...
I was, I was just
trying to find Ciel.
What, is my Lord
actually going to dance?
Shut up!
That's new.
See, it is turning out
to be an interesting party...
Wouldn't you say so?
The young master's
actually dancing.
Blimey, never thought
I'd see that.
Come on, we should dance, too!
The young master
belongs to me.
There's Ciel!
Ciel...!
Ciel!
Ciel Phantomhive.
Alois Trancy.
I swear...
...I will make you mine.
...I will kill you.
Excellent, master...
At last you have found someone
deserving of your vengeance...
Let anger writhe within you...
Let your soul
boil with hatred...
Let us dance...
The dance of death...
the Danse Macabre.
Next time: "Deathly Butler."
If I couldn't revel
in your ravishing revenge...
what kind of black
butler would I be?