Darkness...
Darkness.
Darkness coils its
implacable fingers around me.
I am ever ensnared by it...
Its dark blades
pierce me to the core...
I can feel them drawing out
every last drop of warm blood...
slowly.
Even so...
I choose this.
So now...
I'll scream it.
Rend the darkness
with your voice.
I want this!
I want you!
Here we are, Master.
This morning's tea is Her
Majesty's blend from Ridgways...
Most excellent.
Aw, annoyed now?
No.
Please excuse me.
Hannah...
don't you find fried eggs
rather pathetic?
Nakedly exposed
for all eyes to see.
Indeed, they almost
look like eyes themselves.
But they'll never
become eyes, of course,
or anything but my breakfast.
All that possibility,
wiped out by me.
Hannah.
Yes, truly pathetic indeed.
Hasn't Claude
taught you any better...?
A maid mustn't look
directly at her master.
It's rude.
Do forgive me...
Claude will be most upset
if I don't punish you...
so...
Clean this up at once.
Master, we're receiving
a have a guest today.
Arnold Trancy will be dining
at the mansion with us.
Only because
he wants my money.
This time a priest will
be at supper as well...
It seems he has certain
doubts about your time
"held hostage by the fairies."
No, Claude!
What do I do?!
I changed all the old
loon's decorations...
The nasty curtains, the ugly
rugs, the old knick-knacks!
Please don't worry yourself...
I'll take care of it at once.
Everything.
Really?
Yes... my young highness.
One, two, three...
And now...
I transform day into
night, sugar into salt,
creatures into corpses...
and in this case,
I transform navy into golden.
"That's what makes
a Trancy butler." As you say.
That's my Claude.
As long as I have you, I don't
need those other useless clods.
One thing...
I prefer my roses
displayed like this.
O-lé!
The morons arrive...
I am deeply honored that you
made time in your busy schedule
to come today, Father...
Also...
I appreciate the presence
of the Viscount Druitt.
Of course. It was the
least I could do...
I am happy to oblige.
I owe dear Uncle Trancy
a great deal... Yes.
He lent me help
in trying times...
and when someone does
that, the Viscount Druitt
pays him back twofold...!
My devotion gives rise
to generosity!
Yes, quite.
At any rate, you asked me
to accompany you today because
you find the current head of
the Trancy house suspicious?
Yes.
My nephew, Alois Trancy,
was kidnapped soon after
his birth under
mysterious circumstances.
Out of despair, my
sister-in-law killed herself.
My brother
searched for his son.
He looked everywhere...
And one day,
Alois returned home.
He had a new butler in tow.
But shortly afterwards,
my brother died
of a horrible infection...
Alois succeeded him
as the Trancy family head.
I see.
And the concern
is there's no proof that
he's Earl Trancy's
legitimate son?
That's exactly right...
but I know your holy eyes
will see the truth Father...
And you, Lord Druitt, had close
ties to the previous earl.
I would like you to uncover
who that child really is.
Uncle Arnold!
How good to see you!
Yes, Alois.
Oooh...!
But surely, God, thou has made
a most grievous mistake...!
Placing such great beauty in
someone so young as this boy?!
Yet I shall persevere...
and forgive thee for this
transgression, Lord...!
Amen.
Erm... uh, well...
Oh, my!
It all remains as it
was when Uncle Trancy
still lived among us!
The mansion's glittering
gold...! Bringing the legend
of Cipangu springs
to life again!
Yes...
I haven't changed a thing.
I've preserved it all
since Father's time...
I had to.
I couldn't lose the warm essence
of him the mansion contains.
I can tell you
loved him very much.
For a very long time,
I lived in a village...
The memory sickens me still.
To this day, I do not
know what it was called.
I don't even know how long
I remained there.
They worked me like a slave...
They didn't even
let me go outside.
You poor boy.
There was one other
child who was treated
in the same way I was...
It sounds silly, but I thought
of him as a younger brother.
And then one night...
one dark night...
What's happening?
What is it?
Inside the rippling flames...
the horror of dying screams...
there could only be one thing...
darkness.
There you are!
C'mon wake up.
What's wrong with you?
You can't be...
No...
Please, no...!
Don't leave me alone!
Please don't!
What happened to
the village that night?
That's something
I may never know...
But...
at least my father came
to take me home, finally!
I thought: "At last
I'm not alone...
I have a family to love me!"
Then he...
he left, too.
How terrible for you.
O Lord, I take it back!
I cannot forgive you after all!
Come now, Lord Druitt,
Despair is a sin.
Young man, I pledge
to help in any way I can.
I pray you find
solace in this world.
Thank you very much, Father.
But I know I'll manage.
Because I still have Uncle
Arnold after all, don't I?
Yes of course you do.
Uncle Arnold,
if I may say...
Yes, what is it boy?
Don't lean your face
so close to mine.
You have disgusting
old man's breath.
I can't stand
that damn brat!
Wait...!
Come back Uncle Arnold.
I know you only came here
because you want money.
So here, you can have this!
I have no use for them.
I wouldn't feed a goat
with these moldy old notes.
Let's see,
deeds to some land...
Here, and horses, too.
Take all.
They're yours!
You! Pick all these up.
Look at him, Claude, like
a cow learning to dance...!
What a pitiful sight.
Waiting, Claude.
Master?
I want you to laugh, too.
There's a storm coming.
A storm has blown in.
What brings you to
our door at this late hour?
I've been caught outside
in this wicked storm...
I was hoping I might trouble
you for lodgings tonight.
Look at you!
You're so filthy...
You look just like
a drowned rat!
But still...
You do smell rather nice...
So...
What's your name?
This man will be
staying with us.
Understood, Claude?
Try this one...
Claude's cooking
is simply delicious.
Yes...
it tastes quite nice...
However...
Please observe the speck of
sauce on the rim of the plate.
I assume it would have been
too great an inconvenience
to dab it with a cloth.
My apologies, sir...
I'll clear this.
I didn't realize a man who
doesn't remove his coat at
the dining table would have
such delicate sensibilities.
You flatter me.
Some hot water for you, sir.
May I ask why do you wear
a bandage over your eye?
It's nothing.
I'm impressed that
you can still work.
Hannah.
What are you doing in here...?
Tell me.
I...
I came to change the water.
Oh...?
Or perhaps you were seeking pity
by wearing that silly bandage
and acting pathetic
for our guest.
Get out of here now,
you stupid tart!
Very sorry...
Forgive her, sir.
Are you certain
she'll be all right?
Who knows...?
I don't care for her much.
She's such an embarrassment...
What is she thinking?
Well...
For that matter, I suppose
I don't often know
what anyone's thinking...
So!
What's in that
trunk of yours...?
Clothing...?
Sweets...?
Weaponry?
I'm jealous of you...
I bet you travel to all sorts
of fine places, don't you...?
I wish that I could
travel sometime.
This mansion's so dull!
It's dull?
But I've been told
something interesting
lies under this mansion.
Yes, like what?
We can strike a bargain...
Show it to me, and I'll
show you what's in this trunk.
Just follow me.
There...
That's it.
What, this? It's just tea.
It's "New Moon Drop."
People say that tea leaves
plucked at the full moon
give off a clear,
sweet smell...
These are the opposite,
however, having been plucked
at the new moon...
Their indistinct aroma
can bring a mind to total,
bottomless darkness.
It has another name...
It is called the
"soul's temperature."
Not quite yet.
Oh?
No need to get prickly.
I promise I'll
show it to you...
But one thing first.
That's right.
First, you'll hand
over that trunk.
Sebastian Michaelis!
He's getting away!
Don't kill him!
I want him alive!
Catch him, Claude!
Do you value that
trunk above your own life?
Pity!
Ciel Phantomhive?
I finally have you...!
You're mine!
You're wrong about that.
I would never let
the likes of you touch him.
Somebody as vulgar as yourself,
isn't worthy to come anywhere
near this trunk,
nor will you ever be...
Your mere touch
would defile my young master.
What?!
You put your feet on something
that's meant to carry food...?
What kind of butler are you?!
What kind of butler am I?
Why I am simply one--
No...
it's not quite
time for that yet.
You flee instead of fighting?
I believe I recall your ways...
Turning day into night...
sugar into salt...
navy into golden.
It seems I shall have
to transform golden...
Into black!
It's dark...
Claude, I'm scared!
Lights on!
Go after him...!
Quickly!
No, Claude, not you...!
You can't go!
Master...
Don't leave...
Don't leave me.
Don't leave me alone...!
Please don't leave!
You can't leave me
all alone, too...
Please, Claude...
Don't go!
Of course, Highness...
We're companions.
I am not going anywhere.
Day and night...
Sugar and salt...
creature and corpse.
...defiled and immaculate-
No!
I know that other man
was right...
I am only a
brat--foul and vulgar.
You are more than that.
You are my master.
Oh be quiet...
I know you feel the same way.
Look at me.
I am still
your loyal servant...
There's no need to convince
me of your worth.
I grow hungrier each day...
You'll make
one hell of a feast.
Just forget about it...!
All of you...
You can be swallowed
by the darkness.
Young master.
Now...
young master.
It's time to wake up.
It's been quite a while
since I've seen you all...
Pardon me, but you're
looking at me strangely.
Oh...?
Another butler, you say...?
I know it's warm outside,
but I never thought
it would affect peoples' minds.
I'm sure you agree there
is but one true butler:
Sebastian Michaelis.
Next time: "Solo Butler"
If I couldn't stop a flood
and catch a giant tuna,
what kind of butler would I be?