Hoheo taralna, rondero tarel.
Hoheo taralna, rondero tarel...
Hoheo taralna...
Pardon, master.
I'll change your bandages
if you'll allow me to.
You aren't of any use to me...
Get out and call Claude.
Certainly master.
I'll go at once.
I've seen eyes like that before.
Eyes that make your skin burn.
Excuse me, master...
Might I change your bandages?
That brat...
He could have done
a better job of stabbing me.
Indeed.
He used more force
than he could control,
and that threw
his trajectory off.
If he'd remained calm, he could
have managed a deeper wound.
Interesting...
The way you say that
almost makes it sound
like you wish he had.
No...
It's not that.
It's just that the clumsy
artlessness of the cut suggests
a certain purity.
Purity.
Yes.
Say, do you fancy
the smell of my blood...?
Does it make you want to feast?
Yes...
it certainly does.
Now, if you'll
excuse me, my lord.
What...
what was that?
A smile...? From Claude?
That's...
sickening...
You're out of bed?
Take me...
I need to see...
Ciel...
I need to see
Ciel Phantomhive...
Take me to him!
Come back!
That's my father's!
Cripes...
There's not much here.
Brother...
do you think this is medicine?
Chuck it.
I wonder if he'll be
all right without it...
I mean, do you think
he's going to die?
Eh, I doubt it...
Besides, what do
we care if he does?
He's a dotty old man.
What happened?
It was the baker.
He threw a stone at me.
That bloody sod!
I'm okay.
It's not just him...
It's all of them...
They can...
They can all just drop dead!
As soon our parents died,
everyone treated us
like nuisances.
I wish they'd die...!
Every last one of them!
I'm sure your wish
will come true, brother.
I know it will.
It's gotta...!
After all, you can eat
three kidney pies at a time...
and run faster than
Spring Heeled Jack...
Run, run, run,
run, run aaand...
jump!
Yeah, you can do terrific
stuff, so you'll get
lots of terrific wishes!
Listen...
Luka...
you have to stick with me
always from now on...
If anyone throws a stone
at you I'll throw a pile
of horse manure at them...
Understood?
Yes...
Your...
Highness.
What happened here?
They're all dead.
But how?
That old man
with the medicine...
That sodding baker
who threw stones at you.
And that lady who used to
throw rubbish at our house.
Miz Lila.
And the rotten vicar who
would always spit on us!
And the shoe-shiner
who'd brag about his sweets.
Him too?
All the bounders who were
so nasty to us are dead.
Every last one of them...!
Dead good and proper!
Everyone,
everything, is all gone!
Gone!
Come on...!
With them outta the way, all
their stuff belongs to us now!
Pearls don't
suit you, old lady!
You ever look in a mirror?
Luka...!
It's time to go home.
Luka?
Darkness.
Without a single
beam of moonlight...
So dark.
Luka!
There you are!
I was calling you.
Come on, wake up.
What's wrong with you?
No.
No...
Please, no...!
Don't leave me alone!
Please don't!
Quite a group today.
That's Her Majesty's
spider for you.
Ensnaring hapless innocents
like they're so many flies.
Poor things know
they're caught in his web?
He'll drain them of every
last drop of their purity.
Truly terrible.
Next!
Move on.
Your eyes disgust me, boy...!
When I look at them,
I can scarcely think
of more than filthy rain water
Next!
There are these fairies, see.
All you have to do is
make a pact with them,
and they'll grant
you any wish you want.
Cut it out...
Are you a bloody idiot...?
Didn't you hear what
the old man is
going to do to us?
But...
How do you do it?
A spider's web
wet with morning dew.
Like a veil that
hides your true face.
Hoheo taralna...
rondero tarel.
Useless story.
Is this snow?
Ash...
What is your wish?
Wish...?
What...?
What wish...?
I...
Your wish.
Why would you call me
if you didn't have one...?
Perhaps there is someone
you'd like to get even with.
I hated all the villagers.
But they're all dead...
And I don't care
about that old pervert...
I'll escape...
except I don't have
anywhere to go back to...
nowhere.
In that case...
you have no business
with me, do you?
Yes!
All right then, but you have
to tell me what your wish is.
Well?
As I thought.
If you can determine a wish...
I shall make
a contract with you.
Hold on...!
Tell me, are you a fairy?
I am a demon.
A demon...
Finding a wish.
That became what
I never knew I didn't have...
A purpose for my life.
Another of my
dolls has broken?!
Yes...
I'm afraid that several more
have collapsed from infection,
my lord.
Don't you know how fragile they
are...? Soak the entire room
in anti septic solution!
I beg your pardon, lord...
I've prepared Jim
for you today.
Jim...!
Is that filthy brat really
all you have to offer me?
Is this real?
You're him?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
...Forgive me, father dearest.
Sebastian Michaelis.
Is he a demon too?
Yes, that's right...
It was he who wiped out
your village pursuant to
a contract with
a certain individual.
And who might that be?
Sebastian has already
eaten his soul.
A demon killed him...
Luka.
Now there is Ciel Phantomhive.
He is the human party
to Sebastian's new contract.
With this particular
soul, Sebastian has
a singular obsession...
One fiercer than he should
by rights feel for his prey.
Hoheo taralna...
rondero tarel.
I order you to make
this "Ciel" mine.
Master.
Oh, Father!
Father!
According to your orders,
master, I have freed the boys.
And I've seen
to the inheritance.
Fine.
But what about Ciel Phantomhive?
May I ask a question?
Why would you like to
possess Ciel Phantomhive
rather than kill Sebastian?
Simply killing
him isn't enough.
After death, he would just
peacefully rot into a skeleton
in some patch of earth...
No, that's too good for him...
You see, I want him to know
an agony worse than death.
The boy's the key.
We'll use the 'young master
Ciel' he fancies so much.
Magnificent.
Ciel Phantomhive is mine.
Mine...
and so are you, Claude.
Yes...
Your Highness.
Hello!
Who are you?
What a shame...
Babes in arms are
no fun at all...
We'll do this quickly, then...
Let's see...
Jim Macken...
that's your real name...
My, what a dreary name...
Well, no matter I suppose...
You are at death's grim door...
aren't you?
Now, normally I wouldn't
leave the office just
for something like this...
but, as it happens, we have
a teensy issue with your soul.
This looks bad.
Ugh, I knew it was a demon.
You're not just
a pretty face, then...
Where'd you get
something like her?
Hannah, kill ginger
here, would you?
Hot-blooded little
nipper, aren't you?
I don't want a fight.
I just want t--
All right, then, but I'd better
be paid overtime for this.
Claude...
Don't look at me!
You lot make me sick!
You demon...!
You're just like him!
Yes, Your Highness.
Don't say that!
"Yes...
Your Highness."
Yes...
Your...
Highness.
"Yes...
Your...
Highness."
Yes...
Your...
Highness.
I changed my mind...
Say it...
Now!
Yes...
Your Highness.
Would you do
anything to obey me?
Are you a pet?
My loyal dog?!
I abide by our contract.
I'll make one hell
of a feast out of you.
That's all.
Then look at me like that...
Not the way I would look
at some villager's face.
And not with the craving look
the old man would give me.
Look the way you
did that day...
Like I am all
you care about...
Please, Claude!
Hesitation into resolve...
passion into composure...
love into grave markers...
That, master, is what
makes a Trancy butler.
He's just hungry...
That's it...
I know that well enough.
My feelings are nothing more
than a poorly made sauce
clouding the flavor.
But...
now I'm here.
A little maid like you
should know better than
to go causing me trouble.
What are you trying
to do, master...?..
Why are you here?
Your goal is incomplete.
You do not yet
have Ciel Phantomhive.
It's just you now...
You're all that I have.
Come now, master...
Don't say such
ridiculous things.
Shut up...
shut up...
shut up...!
You're the only one...!
You're all that I have!
Hoheo taralna, rondero tarel...
You can't ever leave my side...!
Never...
not you...
please, Claude...!
Do you know...
I think you...
You're my highness!
What a thing
to say to a butler.
Don't worry, master...
Have no fear.
Your's is a crass soul
who would give his love
to a butler...
I could hardly work up
an appetite for that...
I'll keep you.
I can use your soul...
Indeed, I can.
So that's what's going on.
Yes...
that boy was slated
to die tonight,
but the soul ledgers
weren't affected...
Well...
I did assume that
a demon was involved.
Will you be taking him,
grim reaper?
I just need to keep
the accounts balanced...
I'd just as soon watch
how this all plays out.
You see...
I think it will
be interesting.
So does that mean you have
not taken Sebastian's side?
"Taken his side?" Please don't
insult me with such an idea.
The only true way for me to
prove my love to dear Bassy
is with a death match!
I know it will.
It's gotta...!
You can do terrific stuff,
so you'll get lots
of terrific wishes!
And now...
Shall we discover
your wish, my lord?
How did you enjoy your
first time plunging
a blade into human flesh...?
Dear me, it's not like you
to be so indecisive, master...
Best not to show even
the slightest weakness...
You never know when
a demon might creep
in to take advantage.
Next time: "Hollow Butler"
If my daily fluid intake
wasn't at least two liters...
what kind of
butler would I be?