My master's soul gained control
of Ciel Phantomhive's body.
By doing so, he was able to
enter into a contract with me.
Ciel Phantomhive's soul will
not see the light of day...
It is here, trapped and
powerless within this body.
And so it will remain until
my master's soul is released...
and our contract is fulfilled.
What are the details
of the contract...?
What does Alois Trancy want?
That is a secret
between my master and me.
How presumptuous.
However...
I will give you one
piece of information...
My master does not want
both of you to live...
In accordance with his
wishes and our agreement...
one of you will end
your life as a demon.
The struggle will
end when one of you
claims victory and the
terms of the contract
my master and I signed
have been met...
When this has happened...
my master will agree to release
Ciel Phantomhive's soul...
and after that...
Hannah...
What's to stop us
from killing you?
I will be suffused with
a shade of the noblest blue...
and your precious
Ciel Phantomhive
will come back to life.
This island of death
is a sanctuary for demons.
It seems your rage has left it
in a rather pitiable state,
Sebastian...
You should learn
to control your temper.
You brought us to
this place for a reason.
What do you expect of us?
This is an ideal location
for a battle...
You will engage in
a duel between demons.
How ridiculous...
Duel between demon butlers.
Yes, amusing, isn't it...?
To see two grown men act
like desperate children.
Then what happens?
My wishes will come true...
and when they do,
I'll die for real and Hannah
will eat my soul...
After that, I'll return
this body to you.
Return this body...
Huh.
I did a terrible
thing to you, Ciel.
Both Sebastian
and Claude love you.
I wanted to punish you for
living such a blessed life.
Love, eh...?
How childish.
Huh?
You don't understand
Sebastian at all, do you...?
Have you any idea how
he'll react when he learns
the details of the contract?
No human weapon known
is powerful enough
to fatally wound a demon...
That said...
a wound caused by a demon's
sword will never heal...
The damage done by
such a blow is permanent.
There is no hope for a soul
pierced by a demon's sword.
It will be utterly obliterated.
Now then...
A demon duel with
a single sword.
A singular sword to battle
for a singular soul.
When this is done,
I will sink my teeth
into the young master's soul!
I'll bite hard...
Deep.
And cruel.
The soul is mine!
A small space like this hinders
my ability to move freely.
But I can take care of that.
Let's widen this
space up a touch?
What now?
Come, master!
Damn you, Sebastian Michaelis!
The demon sword...
The Phantomhive soul...
I will have them both!
It's raining...
My, my...
I've already exacted
the revenge I so desired.
With that achieved, I existed
for a singular purpose...
to have my soul
devoured by Sebastian.
But then Hannah and
I made our contract...
and your plans were foiled.
I can almost pity him.
Fighting while
still in the dark.
He battles now not knowing
what will happen when he wins.
...not knowing the
truth of his reward.
It's over...
Your dreams of tearing the
young master are finished.
The young master has...
such...
a sweet soul.
The fight is over...
The battle for his
worthy soul has finally
reached its conclusion.
Even as I wither away...
I can smell his rich,
untainted fragrance.
You think that's the
young master's soul...?
You've got it wrong.
It is Alois Trancy's soul
that trifles with you...
and you'll die
as he intended.
Don't you see?
You've been under his
control this entire time.
Alois Trancy...
It was him?
My spectacles.
What?
I've...
a spare...
in my breast pocket.
You understand.
I've had a very long,
very idle life as a demon...
If Alois Trancy has managed
to spice it up a bit...
then perhaps I
underestimated his soul...
I might have taken great
pleasure in tearing it apart
piece by piece as well...
But now it's over...
Done.
You're remarkably talkative...
considering the
severity of your injury.
Yes...
But not for long, I fear...
My end is indeed at hand.
Well then...
do you have any
last words to speak?
Yes.
Passion into insincerity...
Utter lies into abject truth...
A stray dog of
a boy into an earl...
That's what makes...
...what makes...
a...
butler.
A butler indeed...
but whose butler
did you die as, Claude?
No, Claude!
It's over now.
You're right...
It's all over.
Satisfied?
I don't really know...
I'm no longer
sure how I feel.
But...
But?
Well...
Strange as it sounds,
that's fine with me.
Here we are, Sebastian...
The truth is right
in front of you now...
So what will you do...
when you learn everything?
At last...
we can know happiness.
Oh...
dear master...! Claude
finally acknowledged you.
Hannah...
The terms of the contract
I made with my master
have been suitably met...
All you have to do
now is kill me...
Simply do that, and your young
master will have his body back.
However...
Even with his body returned...
You will find that Ciel
Phantomhive is as good
as a dead person to you.
My master and
I have succeeded...
our work is nearly done.
As for Ciel
Phantomhive, well...
The contract?
Tell me master,
what do you wish?
Do you want Claude's love...?
Or would you like to tear off
his limbs and force
him to serve you?
Did you hear that...?
They're approaching now.
Yes...
in continued pursuit of Ciel
Phantomhive's noble soul.
I've decided...
I know how I would like
our contract to be concluded.
My desire...
is that neither of them
will gain Ciel's soul
You wish for a murder, then?
No...
that's not what I had in mind.
I finally saw Claude's love,
but it eluded me...
I want them to know
exactly how that feels.
She said that, to me...
my master would be
as good as dead.
This isn't what I expected.
Jim Macken...
Luka Macken...
Claude Faustus.
And Hannah Annafellows.
The four of us will
share a great love...
such as the world
has never known before.
Luka...
We're finally together.
Luka!
Brother!
We'll stay together forever...
with Hannah and Claude, too!
Yea...!
I'm not lonely anymore.
That's right...
No more loneliness.
We're home...
We're happy...
At last!
Master...
Master!
I served you even though it
meant becoming a lowly butler...
I remember...
Thank you very much
for waiting, master.
Are you incompetent?
Lord...
what do you mean?
You somehow managed to make
this slop look like real food.
But it tastes like something
found in the rubbish bin.
I do apologize...
I'll bring something
else right away.
You signed an official
contract with me...
Per that, you're now my butler.
I expect you to act like one.
Yes, my lord.
Damn demon...
That's right...
I am a demon.
How could I ever
hope to understand
the taste of human food?
The only taste
I can understand...
is the taste of a human soul.
Good morning, young master.
Would you prefer
to make it even tighter?
No.
I've prepared
your tea, master.
This morning we
have New Moon Drop.
What is my schedule today?
It's open.
It smells quite nice.
Come in.
Er...
pardon, master...
It's the Lady Elizabeth.
She's here, sir.
All right.
Excuse me.
As for the schedule...
I'll decide it.
I want both of you to
attend to the young master...
and make sure Lady Elizabeth
is comfortable.
Okay, Sebastian...
But where are you going?
I have some other
business to take care of.
What kind of business...?
Oi, what's going on here?
Ciel!
I-I can't breathe.
I missed you so much...!
You shouldn't deprive
a lady like that!
And just look at that horrid
outfit...! Not cute at all!
Plain black like that
doesn't suit you one bit!
No, perhaps not...
Maybe I'll change then...
I have done it before.
I don't understand
what you mean...
What is it, Ciel?
I'm confused.
Will you give me the honor
of a dance, my lady?
I'd love to!
Say, Ciel,...
where is your ring?
This music sounds strange.
The gramophone
must be broken.
Oh.
Whatever's the matter?
Oh, hello there,
Phantomhive butler...
It's been awhile.
Hello...
I'm glad to see you
in good health.
Yes, I suppose I should thank
you for letting me slip away...
Still, I went along
with your little charade,
so we're even aren't we?
Yes.
I appreciate it...
and I've brought
something for you.
Easy, Ran-Mao.
My master will be away
from town for some time...
He sent me to say goodbye.
Ah...
I shall miss him terribly.
I have a message from him.
"I thought about killing
you, but I decided it was
too much of a bother...
You can do as you please...
However...
Make certain to
keep out of my sight."
Oh...?
So his memory returned, eh?
That's a happy ending,
isn't it, Ran-Mao...?
So...
he's leaving fair London Town?
What took you
so long, Sebastian?
I apologize.
We can leave now.
Young master...
it's true then?
You're really leaving us?
Do whatever you like
with the mansion...
You're free to stay
here if you want.
Or just burn it.
I don't really care.
What?
We could never do that!
Whyever not?
Because...
this place is
filled with memories!
Memories don't mean
anything in the end...
Or haven't I proved
that much already?
That's not true, Master!
I was curious to see what you'd
do when it was all over...
when the contract between
Alois and Hannah was fulfilled.
I have to admit
you surprised me...
Well done.
I never thought
you'd try to kill me.
I would help you
realize your revenge...
and in return
I'd have your soul.
That's why I served
you as a butler...
why I have remained
by your side all this time.
That's right...
but I'm still
very much alive.
Yes, indeed...
You are alive.
not as a human...
but as a demon.
That day in the maze,
Alois Trancy signed
a contract with
Hannah Annafellows.
As my contract stipulated...
Ciel Phantomhive
will come back to life...
but now he will
live forever as a demon.
That's why I did what I did.
That was quite
a greeting you gave me...
You wanted to kill me
before I awakened eh...?
Before I could live as a demon?
No...
I had something else in mind.
Killing you wasn't my intent...
I wanted to see if you
truly had become a demon.
I see.
You wanted an accurate
assessment of the situation.
A proper consideration
for a proper butler.
So now here we are...
I shall never be able
to devour your soul.
That's right...
but there's more.
I gave you an order while
you were in the labyrinth.
to remain my butler
until you'd eaten my soul.
Indeed.
...I heard your order...
I understood and acquiesced.
I cannot eat your soul.
I am a butler...
now and always...
...for a fellow fiend of hell.
Where shall we go now?
Do you know, I don't much care.
After all, you and I
already know where
we are ultimately
going to end up.
I was always going there, as
a dead human or a live demon.
I feel good somehow...
as if released from a spell
I was under for a long time.
Yes...
and in return for that...
I have been put under
an eternal spell.
You're my butler, Sebastian.
I am simply one hell
of a butler...
for eternity.
And as before,
there is only one answer
that you will give me...
You know it, don't you?
Yes...
my lord.