Young master...
good morning.
I know that smell.
Is it Earl Grey?
Indeed...
My compliments to your
excellent nose, young master...
This morning we have
an Earl Grey Impérial.
It's most excellent, made from
the finest leaves available...
A true masterpiece.
I believe it will be
perfect for you.
Your schedule this afternoon
is like a fresh field
of virgin snow...
Blank as an unlined page.
Today everything
shall be as you wish it.
What of Alois?
Where is he?
Whatever do you mean...?
It was your noble sword
that struck the blow
that felled Alois Trancy.
Is that so?
Does thinking on it
pain you, master?
He died because he
was weak, simple as that.
Oh, such
unwavering confidence!
Here is the nobility of one
who has subjugated others
all his life by right of birth!
Here are the legs
of one unused to walking...
so very slender and delicate.
Smooth skin,
soft to the touch.
Blissful.
What's that?
That...?
Likely just a cat.
That crash was
too loud for a cat...
Strengthen the
manor's defenses!
Indeed...
my young lord.
What a revolting display!
Such a strong kick...
blissful!
Honestly!
I shall investigate it...
First...
Hannah...!
Guard our lord.
Yes.
A storm has rolled in.
Ah, little one...
Fear not...
Master specifically told it
to stay out of his sight...
There's nothing
at all it can do.
The sweetbriars
are looking lovely...
Simply look at these exquisite
flowers, little one...
They are perfect
for my young master.
Yes, they suit my
young master quite well.
Yes, Oh...! It's
just too much!
He's just delicious!
Gorgeous, lovelorn Bassy!
oh...
my...!
Letting that Claude demon go
was a most excellent decision
on my part...
Just look at this photograph!
Absolute perfection!
What...? No...! Not now...!
Don't break on me.
My, when did you get here?
Funny, I was going
to ask you the same.
Well...
perhaps just one more.
Mmm, a marvelous pose.
Bassy...
I must admit, it is rather
odd seeing you prepare tea
just for me...
I, uh...
I'm happy, of course...
But, well, I, uhhhhhh...
A cup of Suutei Tsai,
a Mongolian milk tea
flavored with rock salt.
R-rock salt?!
I've no doubt it will
be wonderfully stimulating
to feel the salt
in your wounds.
Just for you, I've doubled
the amount it calls for...
Doubled it again.
And thought...
why not double it yet again?
On second thought...
I...
Drink up.
The sharp pain of love!
I cannot stand it!
Ahhh!
I see...
So Claude is responsible for
the murder of Alois Trancy.
Yes...
and then he put together
a soul-infusing ceremony...
Two separate souls can
never be completely fused...
but pesky memories
can be overwritten.
Which means that now,
Alois Trancy--
--is the same as
your young master, yes.
Been turned into a ring...
a jewel thicker than
the thickest blood,
more crimson than passion.
I can't say I understand...
Why bother fixating
on some little brat's soul...?
You would make a far simpler,
quicker meal, Bassy.
You sound like
someone else I know.
Just look at his face...
The slack, fatuous features
Claude wears perpetually...
There lies your answer.
Perfectly uniform.
Close-fitting, ivory teeth like
a row of fresh young skulls...
Smooth...
delicate...
enchanting.
Don't gag me!
Apologies, my lord...
Pardon.
I mean really?!
You call yourself a butler...?
Sebastian would never
do something li--
Your contract with him
is but a burden...
like chains
round your wrists...
Continued thoughts
of that demon will be
detrimental to your spleen...
He deserves naught but
your hatred, young master...
Sebastian Michaelis
is your sworn enemy.
I know that.
Break free of your fetters...
Let us sign a contract...
Then we shall get
revenge on that demon!
You presume too much.
I'm only here at all
because I have no desire
to return to that
wretched manor...
Dealing with
Sebastian is my business...
I don't need any
assistance from you.
Oh, don't you?
You're up against
a demon, after all.
You needn't come to
a decision right away.
In this mansion, the threads
of time itself are tangled up
in the spider's web.
He is such a proud young boy...
a truly reckless,
truly defenseless soul.
Ciel Phantomhive's
soul is a fine one ...
Yes a truly fine soul!
B-B-Bassy...
Come Grell.
Let's go.
Ooo-hh...
terribly sorry.
I have an appointment
with my hairdresser...
So...
so lovely!
Come here, camera.
Now, pose!
So you know, I plan
to strike approximately
eight additional
attractive poses today.
I can't pass this up...!
Eight more poses...!
Wait for me!
Thompson and company,
I have a task for you.
I want you three
to see to that demon.
I'm confused.
Why does that butler
call me 'young master'?
Is Alois really dead...?
And was it I who killed him?
And Sebastian...
why would he...?
Master!
Thank you, my lord...
It is your right to thrash me.
Do continue if
it pleases you...
I wish to help.
What now...?
Thrash you...?
Your eye...
Is there anyone in this manor
who's not completely insane?
What, were you going
to stay there all day?
Here we are.
Ugh...!
Oh my, what is
this horrible place?
Oh, but it could work...!
Imagine dear Bassy nude
amid the rubble...! Oh, my!
Oi, guv.
Care for a taste?
Hah...
a joke...! I could
never manage it.
It's been far, far too long...
Got cobwebs down there, I do.
Welcome, sirs, to the cursed
village of Arachnophile.
I thought this place had been
burned completely away...
How is it you're still here?
Ah...
I'm the only one who
was saved from the fire...
Saved by a demon.
He's filthy!
Go on, do it.
Kick 'im some more!
Bullyin' a poor, weak boy!
Ugh, it's slut!
She stinks!
Shut it, you...
Bloody kids.
I'm poor...
but I'm no weakling.
Oh, 'course not.
Sorry dear...
I can see it now.
You're a tough one aren't you.
You can hold your own, eh?
Yeah...
I'm real tough...
I promised my big brother...
I told him I'd be strong!
Everyone, everything,
all gone...!
Everyone,
everything, all gone!
But you seem
like a nice lady...
How about I give you
a free ticket eh...?
Everybody minus one!
What?
Well...
I made me a contract.
With a demon.
The way the boy told it, he'd
made some kinda contract with
a demon to make sure his beloved
brother's wish come true...
The price was
his very own soul.
At first, I thought
it was nothing more
than some silly fairy story...
but then...
The fire came...
Everything the boy
had said was true.
I was the only one
who survived that day.
I've managed on
my own somehow...
But I guess that's
all over now...
Nice meetin' you--
The game is afoot.
Huh?
Oh, nooo...! I've let the
second pose go to waste.
Clumsy, clumsy me!
I swear I won't miss
the next one, though!
Aaah...!
Things are heating up
quite nicely.
Such long, graceful limbs!
Oh, do look out, darling!
What a cruel, insightful gaze.
And his ankles, peeking out
from the cuffs of his trousers!
One exciting
pose after another!
Oh, dash it all...
Is it over already?
Your death scythe...
Now, Grell.
What...?
Certainly you can finish them
off more quickly by yourself.
Please just do it, Grell.
Hmm?
You're incorrigible, Bassy.
Why are you always
doing this to me?
What a warm evening...
Well well, what do you know.
So that's what happened...
There's just no
accounting for demons.
More or less what I thought.
It is?
However...
That, I didn't see.
Um, uh, Bassy...!
You're demoning!
I've seen enough of this.
I have a pressing
appointment...
With a spider.
Grotesque...
What does he think he's
on about, putting his
grubby fingers
all over my dinner?
Wait, Bassy.
Come back...!
I still have at least
two more photographs to take!
He's quick.
Young master.
Whatever's wrong?
I thought I saw him...
I thought Alois
was in the mirror.
Master...
are you hurt?
No, I'm all right.
Hannah...!
Clean this up at once...
I'll take the young master
to his bedchamber--
No, you see to
the cleaning, Claude.
Me, lord?
Now, Hannah...
let's go.
What's this...?
Hannah?
My lord...
I wonder...
What came over me just now?
I hate this mansion...
I want to go home.
To the Phantomhive estate?
I just want...
things to go back...
to the way they were.
Your eye is an odd color...
I can't explain it...
It's nostalgic somehow.
Master.
Watch closely.
I'll show you something.
What on earth is this?!
Is that...
me?
I'm suffering horribly...
But how can I
be watching myself...?
What is that...? Is it...
is it my eye in there?!
That's right...
What you saw was
indeed your own eye...
Sleep well, master.
What a surprise...
I thought you were
spying from a distance,
but here you are
at the front entrance.
My young master's
orders were specific.
He instructed me
to stay out of his sight...
It's certainly no
violation of his orders
if it's only you seeing me.
Now then...
I came tonight to
return this to you.
Another surprise...
A demon terminating a contract
is a most unusual occurrence.
I'm terminating nothing.
You broke the contract first.
We swore to defer our battle
over the young master's soul
until it was fully cultivated.
That is, until after
he had had his revenge.
Our agreement was to use each
other for mutual benefit
until such a time.
My, my...
These spider mites
have discolored the leaves.
It seems my rose was infested.
A regrettable turn of events?
Indeed...
Now both roses are dead.
The contract's terminated...
Hear me now...
Come hell or high water,
I intend to devour
Ciel Phantomhive's soul...
You see...
I know now there's more to it
than its superior flavor...
It goes much deeper than that.
Yes...
In that you are correct.
We demons are
granted eternal life...
However, we grow weary...
We live so long...
far, far too long.
And my young master's life lends
a certain spice to the world
upon which we glut ourselves.
His soul dwells in darkness
and yet remains unstained...
It charms us,
vexes us, tantalizes us...
frenzys us mad...
And now...
Now it's brought us to this.
A broken contract.
A fight between
demon and demon.
It's useless.
The young master is mine now.
For someone who has not
signed a contract with him,
you're awfully confident.
Oh, I'll get a signed contract,
don't you doubt it...
and once I have him,
I won't let him go for a moment.
This dinner knife is a bit
small to cut off your seal
and your arm along with it.
Even so, I'm sure I can continue
to pervert your contract...
It's simple, really.
Sebastian!
Young master...
You're being summoned...
He knows you're here.
You've been seen...
and not just by me...
Such disobedience,
Sebastian Michaelis...
You're a disgrace
to butlers everywhere!
Sebastian, help me!
Please help...!
Sebastian...
If you don't,
I'll climb all the way up!
I'll keep climbing...
I swear I will...
You had better get
here quickly, Sebastian!
I'll climb this thing
I'm Going straight
to the top...
Sebastian.
You're wrong...
I have done nothing
to disobey orders yet.
That's not my lord.
No...
no, it's not.
It's my lord...
Earl Alois Trancy.
All the way up...
See?
I'll fall off...!
I'll do it...!
Do you hear me, Sebastain?!
I'll fall all the way down!
And so, foolish demons
wander, hopelessly lost
in the labyrinth of
a distorted heart...
A convoluted path filled
with the suffocating
scent of roses...
A silverwork treasure chest
awaits them...
My pathetic lord,
sleeping all curled up.
Ah...
the alarm is ringing...
I must go and wake
him immediately.
Next time: "Crossroads Butler."
All right, butlers...
Are you ready...?
Let the games begin!