I'll fall off...
I'll do it!
What is this...?
I...?
How did I come to be here?
And why?
Sebastian?!
I must find some way
to convince you to return
my young master
to me, as himself.
Fortunately, I can
be quite persuasive.
I wouldn't advise killing me...
If you do that...
I'll have to fall.
If you had not noticed,
Ciel Phantomhive's body
now belongs to my master.
Alois Trancy's soul was
taken into Ciel Phantomhive,
absorbed by him...
It waited ever so quietly...
for the proper time
to reawaken.
The soul took advantage
of a weakness
in Ciel Phantomhive's heart...
It used this weakness to
steal Phantomhive's body
using his own eye.
The young master's body
is now Alois's hostage...
So our hands are tied.
I'm going to fall.
I'm going to fall
right off, Sebastian.
There's more to the
situation than that...
Your hands may be tied, but
your hearts aren't, are they?
Prepare yourselves.
I'm sending you on a journey.
Indeed?
Both of you are eager to
retrieve Ciel Phantomhive.
To do so, you must
journey through
the labyrinth of
Alois Trancy's heart,
following the painful twists
and turns that comprise it.
We're being sent
to collect stamps
hidden throughout the garden...
Why, this is
beneath our dignity.
Come to me...!
And you had best
be quick about it...
unless you fancy the
bitter taste of defeat.
I suppose we must.
The only thing I will be
tasting is the sweet flavor
of Ciel Phantomhive's
young soul.
Must you be so
utterly distasteful?
That's what happened?
Alois has taken over my body?
I have his memories?
Memories...
My mansion burned...
No...
wait...
Is that a village burning?
That's not right.
I don't know this place.
It was my mansion.
I was looking for
my mother and father.
A boy...
Who is he?
No...
this memory...
this memory isn't mine.
What've we here?
"Question:...
What is Alois
Trancy's real name?
I believe I can recall
the answer to that...
Alois's real name
was Jim Macken.
Wrong answer...
The garden is enchanted...
It will repel those
who don't belong...
I'm glad to see
it works well.
The answer
"Jim Macken" is wrong...
His real name is Alois Trancy.
How's that...?
I thought that was the
name given to him by
the former Earl Trancy,
the man who defiled him.
True...
but however vile the
old man might have been,
Alois was still
taken by his new name.
Ah, so that's how
this game is played...
A thing is true only if
Alois Trancy thinks it is...
That complicates matters.
I'll be on my way, then.
Lovely...!
Squeeze his supple
flesh tighter! Yes...!
What a perfect shot...!
A perfect pose of agony!
So sexy!
Hello there...
Maybe just...
one more photograph?
You're a grim fellow.
Dead right I am.
"Question:...
What is Alois Trancy's
favorite thing to eat...?
That's easy enough to answer.
Greasy fish and chips.
Foolish...
What is the point of this?
Brilliant...
Just brilliant!
See how well Claude knows me?
He doesn't hesitate...
He knows all of me.
Every last bit, right down to
the deepest, most tender parts.
Perhaps you should
be more careful...
Worried about
this body, are you?
This precious body...!
You like Ciel Phantomhive
more than me, too!
Why is he so special?
What does he have
that I don't...?!
Answer me, Hannah!
Answer me!
"Question:...
True or false: Alois Trancy
died a beautiful death,
as was his due...
His body was never
defiled by Earl Trancy."
What the devil is this about?
The actual answer
would be false.
Though...
the previous question
had nothing to do
with the real truth.
I need you.
I want to make you fly...
You would enjoy
that wouldn't you?
Bassy...!
I'll fly for you.
Farewell my love!
Thought so.
Don't worry dear viewers,
I shall await your kind letter.
My suspicions were correct...
Whoever's writing these
questions is cheating.
Ridiculous...
This is a clown's maze.
I have to remember.
There was a fire.
My parents were killed.
And then I signed
a contract with Sebastian...
I vowed to get revenge...
To punish the people
responsible for it all.
Well, answer me!
What is it?
He's pitching
some kind of fit...
That little brat!
Now, Claude...!
Hurry up...!
I mean it...!
Get up here...!
Stop dawdling...!
I gave you an advantage
in this game.
Such pointless encouragement.
Next up...
"Repeat the phrase 'Yes, your
highness' three full times"...
Yes, your highness.
Silly.
Yes, your highness...
Don't you see, Hannah?
He's still my butler...
He loves me...
He does...
I knew he did...
Claude really does love me.
Master...
then why are you crying?
My lord...
only wait...
I will show you real love.
Young master!
That's right...
Sebastian and I learned that
the Queen was responsible.
She was the target
for my revenge...!
An angel was
involved, as well.
Wait...
What am I seeing...?
The angel is dead...
and the queen, too?
What does this mean?
Have I...
Have I--?
What's happening?
It's the labyrinth...
The maze is transforming!
This labyrinth was specifically
designed to follow
the dictates of
your heart, my lord...
only now Ciel Phantomhive's
will is exerting itself.
His will?!
"Question...
Ciel Phantomhive was wronged...
Has he already achieved
his revenge?"...
This one is different.
Alright...
The answer is...
yes.
Young master.
This is Bitter Rabbit--One
of Funtom's bestselling items.
Master...
you're up there now,
aren't you...?
Waiting...
Yes...
That's how it happened...
I got my revenge.
And as per the contract...
Sebastian took...
...no, he didn't.
"Question...
After the terms of the
contract were met, why didn't
Sebastian Michaelis eat Ciel
Phantomhive's soul?"...
Our contract.
I lost this arm temporarily and
the contract seal along with it.
Knowing all this,
the demon Claude Faustus
seized the opportunity...
He took advantage
of the situation to steal
your soul from me.
A goose?
A silly goose...
of course.
That's my young master.
How dare you interfere, brat!
You bounder!
I'll kill you!!
Please stop this!
You'll hurt yourself as well...
Please be careful.
It's my game...
There are things I want
to ask Claude, too, you know!
Master...
look there.
See, it's Claude...
He's nearing the end.
He's reached the
final question station.
Finally...
at last, I can ask.
Tell me...
Why'd you do it, Claude?
"Final question: Answer this...
Why did Claude
murder Alois Trancy?"
All right...
I murdered him
out of passion...
I killed him for love.
It was the only way
that I could...
I needed you as
a tool to obtain
Ciel Phantomhive's soul...
That's the reason
why I murdered you.
Why...? Why Claude...?
You could have just lied...
You must have figured out how
the questions were created.
But you still...
you still gave that answer.
Sebastian.
That's right...
In the end Sebastian saw
to it that I got my revenge.
Which means that my soul...
Why, Claude?
Young master!
Why...? Why are you
fighting me, Ciel...?!
How greedy must you be?!
Don't you have enough?
Of all people, Claude is dashing
to and fro trying to save you...
Now isn't that rich...?
Can't you even enjoy that?!
What more do you need?
Hush, don't cry.
Let me go!
Piss off!
There's no need to cry...
You'll always be the
best there is, big brother.
Back to the beginning, then.
"First Question"...
Why did Luka sign a contract
with Sebastian Michaelis?"
How should I answer this
when the question itself
is incorrect...?
The underlying assumption
here is quite wrong...
The contract was not
signed with Sebastian...
but Hannah Annafellows.
It was her...
Also known as the sheath
that holds a demon's sword.
Hannah, what is he saying...?
Luka signed
a contract with you?
Yes, master...
My soul desire is
to fulfill your wishes...
I delight in doing so.
In part because that is what
Luka, who sleeps within me,
wishes to do.
Demons have too much time...
I had more than
I knew what to do with.
Human souls were
merely food to me...
They were dull,
nothing more than sustenance...
But then that changed.
Wow, you really came!
I am here...
yes...
but shouldn't you
be afraid of dying, boy?
'Course I'm scared...!
I'm about to piss myself.
Then why call me?
Because, it'll make
my brother happy!
He was different...
Nothing at all like any
of the souls I'd eaten before.
Yes...
your highness.
He was wholly
devoted to his brother.
I was surprised.
I began to feel something
that I never had before.
He became...
precious to me.
Still, I was a demon...
There was only one thing
I could do for him:
Grant his wish as the
contract stipulated.
And grant it I did...
Even if it meant
devouring his soul.
It's you.
You made my wish
come true like you said...
Thank you so much.
Nothing like that
had happened before...
It was the first time a soul
I'd eaten had been grateful.
"Question...
Was Claude Faustus aware
that Hannah Annafellows had
made a contract with
Luka?" The answer is yes.
So...
This Luka boy was in the
habit of calling the master
Your Highness, was he...?
How very fascinating.
Hannah was fiercely
obsessed with the soul
of Alois Trancy's
younger brother.
It was a queer way
of thinking for a demon...
It aroused my interest.
Is it true?
Master, I can still
see Luka within you.
No matter how much
you despised me...
just being near
you made me happy.
That closeness was
almost enough for me.
I love him...
Luka.
But that's not
the whole of it...
I love my master,
Jim Macken.
Now master...
no...
brother...
sign a new
contract with me...
and then...
you'll be reunited...
both of you, inside me...
It's what we desire most,
both me and Luka.
"Final question...
Answer this: why did
Claude murder Alois Trancy?
I'll say it again...
I killed you to
gain Ciel Phantomhive.
I won't fall for
the same trick.
Good evening, Claude...
So nice to see you.
Luka...
Hannah...
I can be one with you...
the people who truly love me.
The people I should
love more than anyone.
It's Ciel!
Sebas...
Sebastian...
I...!
Ciel...
Stop it!
What's happening?
Make him stop...! Do it!
Let go.
Sebastian!
So you fought your
way back at last...
Master.
Heee...
sawww youuu...
He saaaww you.
Youuu let him seee you...
You let him seeee!
Congratulations on the
young master's return.
But he never rescinded the
order for you to stay out
of his sight, did he?
You can't do anything.
Not where he can see you...
Enjoy a little rest;
it's a lovely garden...
I must be going.
Don't just stand there.
You did your part.
You helped me get my revenge.
This is an order...
Eat my soul right now!
Until the final moment when
you've devoured every drop
of my soul you
remain my butler.
Do you understand me,
Sebastian?
Forever yes, my lord.
You want Ciel...?
You do, Claude...
and you, Sebastian.
Well...
That's too bad...
I'll get rid of everyone
who doesn't love me.
Yes...
that's right...
all of you!
Young master...
I've found people
who actually love me...
Luka...
and Hannah.
What's this...? Does he intend
to make a contract with Hannah?
Young master!
Very well then...
I suppose one must focus ones
energy on the proper target...
We have no other choice...
For the moment...
Now...
tell me that you love me.
I love you very much, master.
And...
give me a hug.
Certainly, lord...
Here you are.
This labyrinth is as
persistent as its owner...
and just as frustrating.
That's nice...
Love is so warm.
Master!
Claude...
You ensnared my heart with your
deceptive spider threads.
I wanted you to become
my eternal Highness.
More than anything...
I wanted your love.
The contract is complete.
I have entered into an official
contract with Jim Macken.
And Ciel Phantomhive
along with him.
My master named me Sebastian
after his old family dog...
and Michaelis after the
Japanese word mikaeri,
meaning "repayment."...
A contract is still
a contract, master,
even in another language.
Next time: "Black Butler"
If I didn't follow
my master's orders, what kind
of butler would I be...?
And if I didn't fight for
Ciel Phantomhive's soul--
a soul that is rightfully mine
what kind of demon would I be?