Have a nice evening...
Thank you.
Oh, I do hope they
I do come out well!
How could they not...?
After all you were
the subject, darling.
Surely the likeness can be
nothing short of gorgeous.
Darling!
A lovers' song
destined to end in death.
A lilting melody
singed by sparks of pain.
Wh- -Ellen!
Ellen!
No...!
Ellen...!
Thus the music closes...
The fierce,
fiery finery of death!
This afternoon we have a green
tea from the Kangra Valley...
On the side you will
find a gooseberry
and elderflower jelly.
I suppose it'll do.
I'm glad you find it
satisfactory.
When you're finished,
there is work to be done.
Oh?
People being burned alive...?
Oh, yes...
That's to do with the rash
of crimes in London...?
I'm told there was
another last night.
There was...
Naturally, Her Majesty
grieves for those
who have been afflicted...
and for her citizens,
who live in fear.
Is there something
else wrong, my lord?
"We find these events
most unsavory...
Our course is clear...
We shall again leave the matter
to 'the dog and the spider'."
That's an odd statement.
It sounds as if she's
saying this sort of
incident has happened before.
Yes sir...
And who is this 'spider'?
A mysterious nickname...
"Spider"...
I can't say I've recall ever
hearding of such a person.
There's no use
sitting here, anyway...
We'll see to the
queen's concerns...
That must always
be our priority.
We head for London.
I'll begin the preparations.
One more thing...
Be careful that Madam
Red doesn't catch wind
of what we're doing...
This is the sort
of thing she likes.
We don't need her
poking her nose in.
I doubt there's
any need to worry.
I don't like learning there's
a part of my family's past
of which I know nothing.
It's only natural.
You were forced to assume the
earldom at an early age,
my lord...
Surely there was much your
father was unable to pass on to.
I couldn't have asked for
a better opportunity, though.
If I can resolve a situation in
which my father was embroiled,
word will spread throughout
the criminal underworld
like wildfire.
That should be what I need
to draw them out of hiding.
You intend to use yourself
as bait, my lord?
They began this
by hurting my pride,
but I'm the one
who's going to end it...
I'll drag them all into
the open and make them pay!
Nothing will stop me.
And what do you do if the
culprits have already parished?
Nothing changes...
I'll tear the truth
from their buried,
rotten flesh if I have to.
Simple as that.
Now that's my master...
A true Phantomhive.
The people have a theory...
They say the victims took too
much to drink and combusted.
The Yard doesn't go by gossip...
Go find some evidence!
Yes, sir!
Right away, sir!
--Let's go!
--Aye!
Having a little trouble,
are we, Sir Arthur?
Ciel Phantomhive!
Let's hear about the
investigation so far.
There's no progress
to mention as yet.
So how do these differ
from the previous incidents?
Or perhaps everything
happened exactly the same...
There have been
similar crimes before?
So then you do know.
Actually, not until now...
You confirmed it.
Now that that's settled,
show me the old case file.
There's nothing left of it.
Nothing?
Not a page.
And even if there were,
I couldn't show it to you.
There aren't any records left?
Scotland Yard will find
who's responsible
for this and their motives...
We'll determine how it's
connected to the old cases,
as well.
You aren't needed here.
I hope you're right, sir...
Let's go, Sebastian.
Those round eyes so innocent
of this world's filth...!
That tail, childish
yet somehow noble!
Those paws,
pale-pink and perfect!
Chief Inspector...!
We didn't find
any notable evidence.
Master...
my apologies...
I was distracted
by these charming kittens...
Shall we?
Say good day to
your feline friends.
Who was he, sir?
A menace.
Also known as the
Queen's guard dog...
It seems he's
come back to London.
"The Queen's guard dog...?
Then does that mean he's...
He's a most unpleasant man...
What shall we do?
Well if the Yard is no help...
then there's only
one thing to do.
Startled, the woman dropped
her copy of Bleak House...
"Careful!" she cried.
"You scared the
Dickens out of me!"...
Thank you.
That's all I have
this evening.
That was brilliant...!
Everything from the words
down to the delivery.
You're truly
a comic genius...!
The finest act I've seen
in quite some time!
That might have been the worst
joke I've ever heard in my life.
Which, in itself,
is something special...
I shall have to keep my end
of the bargain, shan't I?
What're you playing at?
I asked for a corpse
from the arson case.
Indeed you did...
And here it is...
in this little vial.
Well, most of it.
I scraped up everything
I could from the crime scene...
After the fire was done with
the victim, there was nothing
left behind for me to
collect but these ashes.
Look, my lord.
Pardon me.
I'm Turner, the photographer.
Excuse the intrusion...
I'm so sorry for your loss.
I've brought the last
picture that was taken
of your dear wife...
Here you are, sir.
She seemed like
such a nice woman.
Our condolences, sir.
She was truly beautiful.
Such a great loss.
My lord.
I've identified the substance
found in the ashes.
It matches the sample we
gathered from the photographer
and his wife.
These are flecks
of magnesium oxide...
a by-product of photography...
It's made from the flash
powder photographers use
to capture their images.
Photography...
eh?
I was able to obtain
information on the import
of such products from Mr. Lau.
Really, a butler and
a chemist, are we...?
Ah, Yes, you're right.
A shipment of magnesium did
indeed arrive at the Docklands
the other day...
Let's see, it was bound for...
a London portrait studio.
From the looks of it,
they're laying in quite a store.
They purchased an
entire ship's worth.
You have me curious...
What are you investigating?
Surely that's more
than they would need
for their flash powder.
Quite...
And in addition, the victims
had something in common...
I've taken a look at the
history of all those burned...
There's a connection
between the women...
They'd all recently had
their wedding photos taken...
Odd, no?
Let me guess:
at Turner's studio?
Let's get moving.
This is no coincidence.
That couple is involved.
Yes, my lord.
Wh...
What are you doing?
You ogre...
Useless, hideous man!
Ever since I made the
mistake of marrying you...
I've waited...
Never a moment
of burning passion.
I'm done taking
portraits of happy women!
There's fire at last!
It's my turn for happiness!
Is that who I think it is?
It's Mrs. Turner from
the photography studio.
Oh, yes...!
I'll find my happiness now!
Master!
That camera must be
her ignition device...!
She has to be stopped.
Capture her!
Yes indeed...
My young lord.
That color...
I've seen it before...
So red.
I thought it was you.
I've been simply
dying to see you...
sweet Bassy!
So, Grell...
You've been pulling the
strings behind the scenes.
I've pulled nothing more than
the red strings of fate
that connect our hearts
together, Bassy!
How could you...?!
I'm so dainty!
Now, now, don't act
so offended...
You struck first.
I just took an
affectionate swipe at you
out of excitement...
I didn't mean any harm.
I was only
following that pig.
You're after her too?
You're acquainted
with this freak then?
Regrettably, yes.
His job is to collect
souls of the deceased.
He's a grim reaper.
A grim reaper...?
It sounds as if you and he
might have something in common.
Really?
There has been
a recent spate of crime...
I imagine that's
what brought him here...
the sudden increase in souls.
I'm sure my workload will
decrease with you on the case,
though...
Se...
bas...
tian...!
At last, our amorous
adventure can begin anew--
Let's spend this--
We don't have time
to fool with him...
Let's go!
Yes sir.
Uh-uh!
Leap through these flames...!
Gather me in your arms and hold
me tight, dearest one--
Excuse me.
Please come back to me...!
Don't leave, Sebastian!
Evacuate the citizens
upwind of the fire!
Right!
This town always seems
so easy to set ablaze.
There she is.
Aw, what a shame...
Did you let her get away?
Hello again, Grell...
Don't you have work
to be tending to?
I am a hunter of love
seeking my favorite game...
That's the only work I care
about right now, my darling.
Besides, it's a slow night...
I only have one soul to reap.
One only?
Margaret Turner's time is up...
At five past midnight...
It says she goes on
a killing spree of sorts...
after which, she burns
herself to death...
She's the only soul
in the ledger...
No one else is scheduled
to be reaped by me tonight...
So I'm as free as a bird.
What about all the people
she's set on fire?
She uses fire of
a very special sort...
When she kills people, their
souls are burned away with them.
Where did you go, Turner?
Up there...
She'll burn everything!
Now you'll all find
happiness too...!
Happiness all around!
Put down the barrel.
Oh so your another interloper
come to take away my happiness!
Have you taken leave
of your senses?
How could you possibly
find happiness from this?
I'll find it...!
My time has finally come.
He told me so!
Master!
Quite a development...
Who knew pigs could
climb so high?
A little brat like you could
never hope to understand
what it's like to be married
to a man you don't even love.
All I want is to feel burning
passion for a man...!
I'll find that, and I'll fry
anyone who stands in my way!
You're absolutely pathetic.
Do something instead
of whining...!
Regrets accomplish nothing...!
Wallowing in self-pity
like that's despicable...
You're no better
than a filthy pig!
Your future's been stolen.
Your dreams have
been shattered...
You're left with
nothing but despair...
Yet you face the
reality and fight...
never once losing
your nobility.
Yes, that's it
my young master...
That's the quality of soul
I want to consume.
A pig...?!
A pig, am I?!
How dare you call me
something so foul?!
Now then I should be hurrying.
I believe you said Mrs. Turner
would burn herself to death
at five past.
Wait a moment.
What are you getting at?
Following my lord's command...
He ordered me to capture her,
so that's what I shall do.
You've arrived at the
party too late for that.
I am never too late to follow
an order from my master...
If I was, what kind
of butler would I be?
Shall the two of us
get going...?
We have a task.
You want me to come along?
You might have noticed
my lord's surly demeanor...
I'm sure he'd make a
rather unsuitable model.
You'd make a marvelous
subject for a photo though,
but if you don't want to...
Allow me to show you
some of the more enticing
shots I've cultivated!
I'll roast anyone
who calls me a pig...
I don't care if you
are just a little boy!
How long am I supposed
to wait on you?
Come...
Sebastian!
Indeed...
my young lord.
You think talking
to yourself will help?
Impossible...!
Who--?
That's my butler...
...and some a freak.
Deadly efficiency.
That's my motto!
Stay out of this,
whoever you are!
What the devil...?
Why haven't you caught fire?
You're using the
grim reaper as bait, eh?
Very clever.
Take as many as you'd like
We ladies ripen like succulent
fruit with every photograph.
I can feel it now.
I'm about to burst like
a bright red berry!
It's pouring...
gushing...
right out of me!
What a marvelous feeling!
So enticing!
So exhilarating...!,
I'm the very Queen of fruits!
The ripest of the reapers...!
Yes!
Well then perhaps
I should bite you.
Please...!
Please!
I expected you sooner.
I'm sorry.
I will burn you, boy!
How could you!
I could have done
much more had I wished...
I have orders to follow,
and follow them I shall.
Where did you come from...?
Who are you people?!
I'm simply...
one hell of a butler
I'm the queen of the reapers,
the ripest fruit there is!
Tell me everything...
From start to finish.
It was him...!
He was the one who
told me what to do...
And if I did...
he said I'd
find true passion...
He said the most
gorgeous men would fight
to the death over me.
And "he" would be...?
The one with the golden eyes.
He promised me!
I don't understand...
Her soul's burning
like her victims' did.
Burning passion!
Happiness!
Hold on...!
--I want to know--
--Master!
My lord...
are you hurt?
I'm fine.
This doesn't make sense...!
It was right here
in the ledger.
How can the soul I'm
to collect just burn up...?
This can't be happening...
It's fundamentally wrong.
I must make my report
to Will, so, alas, this will
have to be our final photo.
Next time it'll be a more
intimate lovers' portrait,
Bassy...!
Toodle-oo!
Bye Bye
I'm sorry, lord...
I know you asked me to capture
the Turner woman, but...
That's all that's left...?
Nothing but a pile of ashes.
I'll inform Her Majesty
that these murders were
the work of a woman
crazed with longing.
I'm continually impressed...
Humans seem to be
capable of anything
when they are
desperate for love.
What a ridiculous waste...
All that for some intangible
concept like love.
Laughable, isn't it sir?
Pathetic as well.
Ah, well...
Not everything
has burned away.
Research this 'spider'...
It may have made
a move during this case.
I want to know everything
there is to know.
Yes my, lord.
Master.
Pardon me for disturbing
you during your sleep.
What is it?
Did you find something?
I visited the Museum.
This book looked relevant.
As we know, there was a previous
instance of live burnings...
During this time, there was
another family working behind
the scenes for the Queen,
like the Phantomhives do...
They specialized in clean-up.
"Specialized in clean-up"
eh...? It's no wonder
Scotland Yard didn't have
any of the old records.
The family head passed away
three years ago...
but as I understand it,
his son has taken over.
They are known as
the Earls Trancy.
Trancy...
Could he be the spider?
By order of the Queen,
we've found ourselves
on quite the perilous
train journey...
I have a weapon perfectly suited
for this particular occasion...
It's hard as a rock...
unwavering as steel...
monumental as a mountain...
Next time: "Terrorist Butler"
If I couldn't whip up a couple
homemade motion sickness bag
or two... what kind of
butler would I be?