My fellows of the deep,
beloved darkness...
Look here.
I present to you
Alois Trancy's soul.
So...
now that I have
obtained this...
what shall I do with it?
Close!
Wide of the mark.
Hannah?
The mansion's décor
seems to have changed.
Precisely correct.
I've transformed the
manor's color scheme.
Once navy, it is
now midnight blue.
The alteration itself
is a subtle one...
Only a select few
will notice.
Their souls may be
fundamentally different,
but look closely and you
will find a commonality.
The pasts that color them.
And that...
is most useful.
Interesting...
so this is their move.
Trouble sleeping, my lord?
A bit, perhaps...
Yes.
It's this business
of killing someone...
it doesn't play out
as one expects.
I had thought the
process would be an easy one...
But as it turns out, I find
it difficult to kill like you,
without hesitation or honor.
I consider that
a high compliment, my lord.
Tell me a story so
I can fall asleep.
Well...
will a message from
Her Majesty do?
There's been a spate
of strange crimes in
the London area recently.
It seems someone has been
gouging out people's eyes.
The victims aren't all
of the same class,
but every last one
is a young boy.
Eye gouging.
How perverse.
Wait no, listen to me!
You don't understand...
You're being
tricked by a demon!
Can't you see that
we're basically the same?
Is there something
the matter, master?
It's nothing.
I don't know!
He just up and stuck
his fingers in me eyes...
Everything went red...
Now I can't see nothin'...
nothin'!
Can you describe
your attacker?
He was just a kid...
'Bout the same
age as I am...
Only this boy
looked plenty rich.
A boy?
That bloody bastard!
Sebastian.
Yes.
A demon has spent
much time building up
that soul stitch by stitch.
And now I intend to steal it.
But I must do so respectfully...
stitch by stitch.
We have several
witness reports.
Without exception,
they describe the attacker
as a richly dressed
young noble.
I'm being mocked, Sebastian.
Mocked by whom, master?
Look.
I'll draw a line
between the Phantomhive
and Trancy estates...
Like so...
Then connect the various
scenes of the crimes.
A spider web...
Obviously, he's behind this.
It may be possible that his
butler is acting on his own.
So he survived...
He's persistent,
I'll give him that much.
Young master...
Trancy...
he is still alive.
Sebastian, a butler always
answers his master's questions
truthfully and
without hesitation...
Am I right?
Quite right, lord.
You aren't hiding anything
about Alois from me, are you?
No...
I am not hiding
anything about Alois.
In that case--
The spider butler?
No...
Not now.
Please stay in here.
Why?
It's just for a bit.
You mustn't set foot
outside of this box...
Please, lord...
Stay put.
Fine.
First they lure us out here
with orders from the queen...
That's just the start.
Next, they rely upon
the ones sure to show up
whenever there's
a soul-related issue.
Reapers.
Ugh...!
Come on...
You've got to be kidding me.
Bloody hell.
It's totally useless now.
Forgive me.
I don't believe
we've met before.
We haven't...
Hi.
The name's Ronald Knox...
The next diehard Reaper!
Yeah...
sounds bleedin
ridiculous, I know...
It's just old man
Sutcliffe insisted I needed
a catch phrase...
I had a bird from
General Affairs come up
with something for me.
Oh, I shouldn't
worry overmuch...
both you and your
silly little catch phrase
are destined to be short-lived.
I assume you lot have gotten
involved because of recent,
unusual soul movements...?
Is that it?
Perhaps the soul
of one Alois Trancy
has proven unrecoverable,
for instance...
Eh?
Perhaps so.
I might have guessed
you'd be involved in this...
And here you are.
Hello Sebastian.
I've felt this before...
I was trapped someplace
like this for a long time...
I know I've
forgotten something...
but I can't figure what.
Whatever it is,
Alois and Sebastian know...
I'm sure of it...
I'm the only one
who doesn't know.
What the--?
Can't you see
that we're the same?
Sod off...! I'm nothing like
you, you vile piece of filth!
You mustn't set foot
outside of this box...
Please, lord.
Bloody sod off!
Damn you...!
I'm the one who gives orders!
Go play at home, kids!
Hey!
You're a kid, too!
Yeah!
Go home!
What a bother.
Working overtime yet again...
All thanks to Grell!
So it's true.
Alois Trancy is dead...
Which means this
is the butler's game.
The spider's thread twines
around a snow-white soul...
One stitch at a time...
Row by row...
...until the web is complete.
Where are you Sebastian...?
I'll find you...
I will learn your secret.
Alois...?
There's no end to his mockery.
Come back!
A dead end...
That's as far as you--
Alois Trancy, there he is!
Idiots.
You're from Scotland Yard,
then...? Well, go after him...
He's escaping.
All right, Trancy.
Don't try to fight us.
What, wait you
think I'm Alois...?
Get your facts straight...
He's right over th--
Let's take him in.
Wait...!
Let me go this instant...!
Who do you bloody
people think you are?!
It's the maid
from the Trancy manor.
Look closely.
Are you quite certain?
Yes...
That is my master...
That is my master,
he is the Earl Alois Trancy.
Are you mad?
Forgive me for saying so,
but he seems to be
an extremely troubled youth.
It's a tragic tale...
My poor young lord was
subjected to repeated abuse
at the hands
of his late father.
The abuse took a toll on him...
I'm sorry to say it
affected his mind.
He despises the mark
carved into his eye
by the previous Earl Trancy...
Any time he sees a boy who
resembles his younger self,
that hatred manifests
itself like some monster...
It whispers...
"Take out their eyes."...
"Take out their eyes."
He took mine as well...
That's why I wear this.
How dare you, vile witch!
His eye is the best proof
of his identity.
Remove the patch from his eye.
Stop this!
No...
You're wrong...
It's a sign of my contract.
My master is also
a victim in all this...
Please I beg you to show
him whatever mercy you can.
Take him in.
Let me go...! ..Stop this!
Sebastian!
All right!
Now then, let's
get this over with...
You can bet your ass
I'm not working overtime.
Against two reapers,
even I'm at a disadvantage.
Blundering little fool...
I don't suppose it's
your intention to fell me
with your death
scythe, as well.
Oh...
did I take it too far...?
Right.
My mistake.
I'm at that
mischievous age, you know.
A grim reaper must always take
care to judge every situation
swiftly and accurately...
Are those spectacles
just for show?
Sir, he's getting away.
My spectacles...
Where are they...?
I can't see.
Pardon sir...
Shouldn't we stop him?
You fail to fully understand
the great importance
of a reaper's spectacles...!
I'll have your scythe!
Oh dear...
I don't even know
where to begin.
Finished.
Ciel Phantomhive...
I'll ensnare you
in my web...
Pierce your skin
with my teeth.
And while you
writhe beneath me...
I'll suck out that
delectable soul of yours.
Why not start by
telling me your name.
My name is Ciel Phantomhive.
Really, treating a nobleman
like a common criminal...!
What gives you the right
to do such a thing?
The Queen...!
Just get word
to her majesty...!
Or you can even contact
Sir Arthur if you have to.
They'll corroborate ev--
The poor lad's quite
far gone indeed...
Administer the
special treatment.
The world...
It's falling away...
Everything...
I apologize for not
simply sending someone
along to fetch you, Sebastian.
No need for apologies.
I found your invitation
easy enough to understand.
We're standing in the
exact center of the web
you lot so carefully created.
I am...
Ciel...
Ciel Phantomhive...
I am the Queen's...
Her Majesty's...
guard dog.
I don't have
a mother or father...
I lost them.
And how did you lose them?
The mansion...
it burned...
Indeed...
it burned to the ground.
The village you
grew up in burned.
I ran...
I ran down the corridor.
That's right...
you ran.
You ran down a path.
You ran through the village...
and then what did you find?
I found...
my parents...
They were dead.
Yes...
You found your brother...
You found your brother,
and he was dead.
My brother?
You found him...
and then what happened?
The old men...
the old men took me away.
Yes...
The old man took you.
He humiliated me...
The Earl Trancy did.
Tran...
cy...
That's right.
The sheath that
holds a demon's sword.
What I don't understand
is why a being so powerful
would be obeying
someone like Claude.
Claude is...
We have a contract...
It doesn't matter one whit
if he's taken from me.
He's still my young master.
None of you can ever
hope to have so much
as a taste of his soul.
First navy...
and then midnight blue...
There are...
two extremely
similar memories.
True...
none of us can ever hope
for so much as a taste...
Not while he's still
entirely your young master.
After that...
I...
I made a contract
with Sebastian.
Yes, someone made a contract
with a demon named Sebastian...
and then Sebastian
started a fire.
A fire...
Yes...
Sebastian made a contract with
your younger brother Luka...
And burned down your village.
Luka...
village...?
That's right...
Sebastian Michaelis and Luka
entered into a contract...
And you lost him...
Your only brother.
My brother...
Master!
Master...
Don't touch me!
My lord.
It was you all along,
wasn't it...?
You killed my parents!
It was you...!
Just admit it!
I didn't predict you
mixing their memories...
Your intention, of course, was
to merge the two soul as one.
That's brilliant.
It never occurred to me.
He's soaked to the bone...
What, did you dip him
in some sort of medicine
in order to confuse my master?
He's asked a question, master...
Shall I answer?
No, there's no need for that.
Yes, I know.
This is an order...
Leave now and
stay out of my sight!
Didn't you hear him...?
A master's orders are absolute.
Are you all right?
I'm...
so weary.
Yes.
I...
I want to sleep.
Yes indeed...
my young highness.
I've delayed my duties...
Dinner should have been
prepared some time ago.
And now...
look what's happened.
Dinner must be made
as soon as possible...
but there's one thing
to do first...
I am a Phantomhive butler.
I must clear the spider webs.
That's plain.
You've returned.
Welcome home.
Golden into navy...
then navy transformed
into midnight blue...
and next...
Alois Trancy into
Ciel Phantomhive.
That makes...
one hell of a butler.
Draw him a hot bath
immediately.
Yes sir.
He'll catch cold
like this...
We need to warm up the young
highness--no--- young master.
See to it.
Ciel Phantomhive was in need
of a target for his revenge...
In the end, that target
was Sebastian Michaelis...
I see...
Rather amusing, really.
Next time: "Zero Butler"
If I couldn't handle this,
what kind of butler
would I be...?
Certainly not
a Phantomhive butler!