It was another ordinary day
in the same ordinary room,
and young Alice was
growing rather bored.
The day dragged on.
Her financial report was
a dreary thing containing
no murders, violence,
or tragic partings...
Nothing interesting at all.
What was that?
Did you say something?
No, my lord...
Nothing at all.
Very well, then...
Bring the tea.
Certainly, master.
What on Earth was that?
My eyes are
playing tricks on me!
Oh dear, look at the time...!
We've fallen two minutes, forty
seconds behind schedule already.
What...?
Why can't I catch him?
To think she fell
for such a trick.
She pretends to have wits,
but she can be quite thick...
Pardon...
what I meant to say
was, "Poor Alice!
Whatever shall become of her?
I do so look forward
to finding out."
What is this place?
I don't recall ever seeing a
room like this below the manor.
This one's locked as well.
Oh dear, oh dear!
I'm late!
I'm late...!
So very late!
Stop this instant!
Three minutes,
ten seconds late.
That git...
He flat-out ignored me!
He ignored me and
he locked the door!
Aww...!
Look...!
Isn't it adorable?!
Quite so, my lady!
I know that voice...
Alice!
I... er...
You look startled!
But surely you recognize
my lady, the Mouse.
I am her maid, the Dodo.
So cute, so cute, so cuuuuute!
Now, why are you wearing
such plain clothes, Alice?
They're not the least bit cute.
It's what I always wear...
but more to the point,
who's this Alice?
Come now, don't be
such a silly goose.
You're Alice, aren't you...?
My teacher at Mouse School
told me, when in the country,
do as the country folk do...
And if you're in Rome,
do as the Romans do.
And if you're a mouse,
stay far away from cats!
I'm afraid I didn't
quite catch all that...
Something about us
being in Rome?
What are you on about?
We're in Wonderland,
not Rome, obviously.
Now, once you're properly
dressed, we'll have some tea.
What do you mean, "Wonderland"?!
What?!
What the devil's happening?!
Um...
would you care for some Eat Me?
That's what this little
cake is called, you see.
Simply adorable!
It doesn't look like any cake
I've ever laid eyes on...
You're sure
it's actually edible?
I'm told its flavor
is most amusing...
I have the utmost confidence
you'll enjoy every crumb of it.
Lovely...!
Let's eat it!
Lizzie, wait...!
Be careful.
No!
It's lovely indeed...!
Oh and the flavor!
It tastes of lemon meringue
pie, gâteau au chocolat,
Victoria sponge cake, scones,
cottage pie, and roast hare,
with just the slightest hint of
lobster curry for good measure.
Sounds tasty.
What's wrong...?
Do you feel all right?
What is it, Lady?
It's...
it's just...
I have a curious feeling.
Lizzie!
What happened to me?
Oh, my Lady Mouse!
Lizzie!
I cannot possibly
be cute if I'm this big!
Lizzie, please stop crying!
It doesn't matter a whit
if you're big or not.
You are still adorable
as ever, my lady!
I shan't be able to wear the
boots I purchased yesterday...
And they were ever so cute!
Should that really be
your main concern right now?
Let's see...
Will something here help?
Um...
Perhaps "Drink Me" will.
That wasn't there before!
How can you be certain?
Perhaps you didn't
look closely enough.
Let's try it.
I'll do anything I have
to save my lady...!
I am her dodo maid...!
It's my duty!
Very well.
Lizzie...!
Here, drink this!
It's tiny!
Tiny!
I'll do it...
I shall drink this
strange potion
in the name of
all things adorable!
My lady the Mouse often
found herself in hot water
when she failed to listen to
others and tried to squeak by
on her own wits.
The journey through Wonderland
has only just begun...
and I fear our poor
little Alice may have
her work cut out for her.
Alice...!
We're over here...!
Row quickly, c'mon!
She's returned to
normal--normal size, anyhow.
Catch...!
Row...!
Catch...
Catch...!
Row!
Row...!
Catch...!
Row!
'Ello, Alice!
You're looking right knackered.
Don't worry.
Shore's not far off!
No need to be
looking so glum.
We're all smiles
here, we are!
Speak for yourself.
Tell me, what's on the
other side of this lake?
Lake?!
Oh, I say!
Is this a lake?
The sea, I thought.
Was that a mistake?
You'll have to forgive 'er.
This is clearly a river.
I've known for a while
that we're on the Nile!
The Nile?
So will we meet a crocodile?
That's just a whim.
They're all in the Thames.
Just give it a break
for heaven's sake.
"Splashing of water...
as the great frog
makes his jump...
into the old lake."
You mean this place
truly is a lake?
Not the sea.
It was a mistake!
Your wits have gone!
Put your thinking caps on!
The only place
this wet is the Amazon!
Bloody dodos!
Would you quit
spouting all that rubbish?
But... um...
I'm the only dodo here...
I'm sorry.
You can say whatever
you like, of course!
So sorry!
Look...!
I see the White Rabbit
He's amazing!
See how fast he's running?
This must be land,
and not a lake after all!
One thing we know for certain:
if a rabbit is in the lead,
a turtle is sure
to follow soon!
Stop at once, Sebastian...!
You are not leaving me here!
I'd recognize
that voice anywhere.
The Puppy!
Look sharp, you two.
Sir...
yes, sir!
Why all the fuss if
it's only a puppy?
Here he comes.
Hold on to your hats!
That is no puppy!
Oh dear, oh dear!
Alice!
It's salty...
The ocean...?
Oh, right...
it's Lizzie's tears.
Sebastian...
Though Alice claimed
not to care for the water,
many suspected that she
avoided it because
she couldn't swim a stroke...
However, she did excel
at being kidnapped,
attacked, and drowned.
Frankly, she might have had more
consideration for her rescuers.
I'll catch cold
if I don't dry off...
I need a change of clothing.
I had no choice.
I am not dressed like this
because I want to be!
And who might you be speaking
to, my playful little robin?
I have so looked forward
to meeting you.
Unhand me!
Playing coy, are we?
How charming...!
Now...
stop fighting and dance
with the Mock Turtle.
Not a chance!
Oh...! This is terrible...!
You won't join me
in a dance...?
How can you be so cruel?
When it's so blatantly
obvious you dressed
in such a pretty
frock to seduce me!
I am not seducing you!
Ah...!
Can this dear little
robin be forgiven
the un-robinlike sin of pride?
No...!
I fear not.
Even if Her Majesty
forgives it, I never shall!
And now, my lady...
your hand, please?
Wait a moment...
There's a queen in
this country as well?
But of course there is...
The Queen of Hearts is
a woman of exquisite beauty
and great charm...
You wish an audience with
her...? Then be a good girl.
Now, lady, may I
have this dance?
Un...
deux...
troi...
Un...
deux...
trios...
Very good...
You're doing splendidly.
May I inquire when this
humiliation will be over?
When your dancing is as
pretty as your frock...
robin.
Dancing is an essential skill
for a maiden to posse--
Stop there.
We'll go back
to the beginning...
At this rate, you shall never
be able to meet Her Majesty.
Although I must confess
I'd love to dance
an eternal waltz with you, my
scrumptious little pound cake.
Now, lift up
that pretty face...
Show everybody at the ball
how ravishing you are.
Bugger...
This is disgraceful.
How is it disgraceful...?
Flowers were meant
to be admired.
The more people who see them,
the more beautiful they become.
Sebastian?!
You mustn't allow yourself to
be distracted, sweet robin...
Now...
concentrate.
I'm finished dancing...
Let me go...
I have to find him
and follow him!
My lady...!
Why chase a rabbit,
of all things...?
Because...!
Well...
I...
Yes?
It doesn't signify.
Now stop spinning me!
But I can't.
I must keep going...
and even if I could stop,
I wouldn't!
What?!
It's too glorious to
stop...! Yes, that's it!
This spin is a metaphor...
The physical reflection
of my feelings for you.
Becoming...
dizzy...
Can you feel the
transcendence?
I can almost see
a flock of angels
flying through the night sky!
You are the fruit
of paradise lost!
I would give anything to
spend the rest of my days
under your spell, admiring
your heavenly beauty.
Please stop now...
I feel sick.
I shall show you...
You will feel the true depth of
my feelings...! Lobster...
Quadrille!
Her body was slender as a twig
and as light as a feather.
When thrown by an
overexcited dance partner,
she could go
quite a distance...
And so Alice flew
far, far away.
So beautiful!
Ciel...
in Wonderland.
Where am I...?
The air is so--
What is this...?
A potato?
What is this place?
What a strange
question to ask...
This is my palace.
I am the duchess...
and this majestic personage
is my esteemed cook!
Turmeric, coriander, cloves,
cinnamon, cardamom, cumin,
fennel, anise, caraway...
and most important of all...
Spicy black pepper!
I've only begun...
The ultimate curry will
not be perfected until
I have added another
three thousand spices!
Excellent!
I would expect
nothing less from you...
And now our final act...
the kitchen maid Alice!
Enough of this lunacy!
Come now, why are you so upset?
Have you been eating
too much chili powder?
That simply won't do...
Less chili powder, more ginger,
and most importantly...
Black pepper!
Yes!
That's it!
Feel the invigorating
spice of Mother Nature!
Would you bloody stop?!
Oh, I'm forgetting
one member of the household.
Mee-ow!
Oh lovely.
Another one...
Just what I need.
When did the
perverted freak get here?
Meow.
What are you on about?
It's always been here...
And it's a Cheshire Cat,
not a freak.
Meow!
Meeoooow.
Well, I've never heard of
a cat that grins like that.
Ridiculous.
All cats grin...
You don't know much about
anything, do you Alice?
Meow.
Cats are no
different from people...
If you only treat them kindly,
they will gladly offer you
their affection in return.
Quite right, quite right...
and most importantly...
Black pepper!
I thought I told you...
To stop it!
The relationship between
a master and her servant
is built upon the giving of
kindness and affection...
Why, even a high-born Duchess
such as I and a lowly
kitchen maid such as
yourself might develop
a deep friendship that
transcends station.
Bravo, Duchess, bravo!
Talking to you is pointless.
I'm leaving this place!
Maid!
Wasting food of any kind
is absolutely unacceptable!
You must heed
the duchess's words...
Every morsel that we receive
is a gift from the gods ...
We cannot waste even one
grain of black pepper.
You need to be punished...
Cook...!
See to it at once!
Jo ajna!
Take that!
It's a spicy curry bun
I prepared in advance
for just such an
occasion as this one.
If you already made it, what
were you mixing all the spices?
Never mind such
trifling details.
The important thing now
is that you eat.
Well, Alice...?
My cook makes extraordinary
curry buns, do you not think?
That's a surprise...
It's quite good, actually.
Oh my, is something amiss...?
Stomachache, perhaps?
I might know.
Is this like what happened
to Lizzie earlier...?
She ate strange food as well.
Oh no...
What's happening?
We must help her!
Or we could run.
Precious lives
were lost today.
I'd like you to erect
a gravestone for them.
Jo ajna...
One other thing, Duchess.
There isn't much time before
your next appointment...
You've received an
invitation from the queen.
All right...
Then, let us be on our way.
Farewell, Alice!
Where are you going?
Come back here and
return me to normal!
In through the roof, then out
through the roof again...?
What dreadful manners...
Poor Alice's appearance had
become exceedingly embarrassing.
However, much to her chagrin,
still greater disgrace
awaited her in Wonderland.
I cannot believe the
nerve of that butler.
Leaving his master
without permission!
He'll notice me
then simply ignore me...
What happened to the
"butler aesthetic" he likes
to talk about, so bloody much?
You there, in the Eiffel Tower!
Halt at once!
What's that?
No, no, not up there.
Look down here...!
Here...!
In the shadow
of your right shoe!
And who are you?
A Lizard policeman who
happens to be passing by...
Pleased to meet you.
I've been looking all over
for the White Rabbit...
Have you seen him anywhere?
So, you got
separated from him...?
That means you're
lost here in Wonderland...
This is serious.
Well...
I suppose so.
It will be all right...
Not to worry...
I'm here to help you,
young Alice.
Well...?
Do you know the way?
Hmm...
Yes or no?!
Hmm!
...I'm terribly sorry.
What a blunder...
It seems I've
brought the wrong map.
Do you always go about making
promises you can't keep
You should check inside your
hand before you get yourself
into more trouble
than you already are.
My hand?
What on earth are
you talking about?
What's this?
It's a magic candy that
will make you feel quite nice...
If you eat it, something
interesting is sure to happen.
True...
It seems something interesting
always happens when
one eats or drinks
in this place.
But will I grow
larger or smaller...?
Either way, I'll be able
to get out of this building.
That's the ticket...!
Go...!
You can do it!
Hang in there, Alice...!
The world is yours...!
You can do anything
you set your mind to...!
Go, Alice, go!
What now?
Oh, dear...
she's let that lizard talk
her into eating the candy...
Honestly, Alice,
such gluttony...!
What just deserts...
ahem...
I mean, adventures, lie
in store for our heroine
as she travels forward?
What the devil is happening?!!!
Alas, we must wait
until Part Two.
Yet to come...
advice from a
mysterious Caterpillar...
a mushroom that toys
with both body and mind,...
a reunion with
the Cheshire Cat...
and a Hatter's mad tea...
Never a dull moment,
dear Alice.
Next time on Black Butler...
Ciel in Wonderland...
Part Two
You see, I am simply one
hell of a White Rabbit.