NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order to
prevent his transformation
into a Victor, Kazuki,
Tokiko, and Gota
headed towards Newton
Apple Academy for Girls,
where Tokiko originally
retrieved the black Kakugane.
Meanwhile, at the Alchemist
Army headquarters,
a Kazuki re-extermination
squad was
formed, along with
Victor search squad.
The re-extermination
squad, which
consists of Hiwatari,
Negoro, and Ikusabe
were confronted by Papillon,
who is also after Kazuki.
In order to learn where
Kazuki was headed to,
Papillon battled Ikusabe.
Meanwhile, Hiwatori
and Negoro caught up
with Kazuki and the others.
-Unless I move forward, my
life, and the lives of the ones
I care for will be over.
So let us pass.
Just move out of our way.
-There's no way in hell.
-Here he comes!
-Heh.
-I must admit, Homunculus,
you're pretty good.
Unfortunately, you can't seem
to shake your exhaustion.
Right now my only desire is to
become more powerful and fight
against an entity stronger
than a Homunculus.
It's time I put an
end to this fight.
-It seems you don't get it.
I've already figured
out the weakness
of that spear of yours.
-My Gekisen has no weaknesses.
This rapid regeneration
is unbeatable.
[scream]
-High speed automatic
restoration means its speed
and timing cannot be
controlled by the user.
Whatever the circumstances,
the restoration
will start instantly.
All I need to do--
-Pappy!
-Is stop it in its tracks.
-Huh?
-By placing a foreign object
just in the nick of time.
And the restoration fails.
-You bastard!
-So, you want to
fight an entity more
powerful than a
Homunculus, right?
If I'm in the mood, then
I'll fight you later.
Until then, I might
suggest you try
becoming a little bit stronger.
[scream]
-Yeah, you did it, Pappy!
Wah!
Pappy!
Are you all right?
Is everything OK?
-Yes.
I'm magnificent.
-Is this really a time
to be striking a pose?
That muscle man is gonna
restore himself any minute now!
PAPILLON: It's OK.
-Huh?
-Even if the main
spear isn't damaged,
without the spear in
his hands, there's
absolutely no way that
he'll be able to activate
the rapid regeneration.
-What do you mean by that?
-The spear will not know
whether he is injured or not.
If it can't detect
his injuries, then it
won't know he needs healing.
In other words, you can now
pronounce me the victor.
[laughter]
-I really didn't think
you'd do that, knowing it
would destroy us both.
-Destroy us both?
Are you kidding me?
No matter what it
takes, I am determined
to reach Kazuki Muto.
-Is your goal really
that important to you?
Tell me now.
Is it?
-I guess so.
Now, a promise is a promise.
Let's hear where
Kazuki Muto is headed.
That was our
agreement, wasn't it?
-Newton Apple Academy for Girls.
That's where they are going.
PAPILLON: I see.
-But I bet it's too late.
-Why is that?
-Surely by now,
Hiwatari and Negoro
have already disposed of them.
[groan]
-So that's the situation.
Did you get all that, Ouka?
Look into it right away.
-Hm?
PAPILLON (VOICEOVER):
Kazuki Muto
isn't the type to
die that easily.
-You should be more careful not
to use too much firepower, sir.
-Oh, shut up.
It's best to just
finish off their type
as quickly as you possibly can.
-Where are you going?
-I'm going back.
I'll leave finding
their Kakugane to you.
-Understood.
-So who's the guy
on the other side?
-Oh, he looks handsome.
He's totally my type.
Tonight
-Shisui Hayasaka.
Until just recently,
he was an LXE Familiar.
-I see.
Well, I wonder if
he'll be of any use?
-Victor.
-Yes.
The mo important mission right
now is to hunt down Victor,
and to eliminate him
as soon as possible.
And for that battle, we're going
to need your help against him.
-And Kazuki?
Will Kazuki Muto be
involved as well?
-He will not be involved.
SHISUI: Kazuki.
[beeping]
-It appears that we
have located Victor.
-They're here.
The Alchemist
Warriors have come.
-Tokiko.
Tokiko.
Tokiko!
Thank goodness.
You're conscious.
-Where's Kazuki?
G-- Gota?
-I can't find him.
It seems like after
the explosion,
we were all blown into
different directions.
-We must find Kazuki before the
re-extermination squad does.
There's no time to
be resting here.
-Tokiko.
Please, just worry
about yourself
before you worry about Kazuki.
You received the main brunt
of Warrior Chief Hiwatari's
attack.
I mean, it's amazing that
you're even alive right now.
-Let's go.
NEGORO: So you two
are still alive.
Where is Victor Three?
Is he alive as well?
-Where-- where are you?
NEGORO: Although you're
not my primary target,
eliminating you is also
part of the mission.
-Tokiko!
Gota!
Where are they?
-Damn you!
You peeping Tom!
Are you all right, Tokiko?
-Don't worry about me.
He's coming back.
NEGORO: What are you aiming at?
Buso Renkin of the Ninja Sword,
also known as Secret Trail.
For your information,
whatever this blade cuts,
it becomes my secret path.
-Gota, are you all right?
-I'm OK.
Stand back and let me
take care of this guy.
-So then, you're protecting her.
Very well, then.
It'll be much easier for me
to defeat my prey one by one.
GOTA (VOICEOVER): Dammit.
Once he dives in, there's
no way to track him.
Think.
Where's he going to attack from?
With that ability, it's
unlikely that he'll
attack from the front.
He's probably going to aim for
the blind spot, like before.
Is it the back, or from below?
Or is it from above?
Motor Gears,
Knuckle Duster Mode!
-Stop!
Gota, look out!
GOTA: A trick?
Then that means he's--
-Tokiko!
-Thank you, Gota.
-I'm-- I'm sorry.
-Hm.
Impressive.
-Get back here!
I'm not letting you go.
I'm coming in with you!
NEGORO: Unfortunately
for you, this path
is reserved for me alone.
No strangers.
Not even a speck of dust
can go through this pathway.
Damn it!
Wait.
Not even a speck of dust?
Then why is it that his clothes
are able to make it through?
Does that mean his
possessions are the exception?
Or maybe--
-Hey.
You were only targeting
Tokiko from the beginning,
weren't you?
NEGORO: What a silly question.
You said you were
going to fight me
in order to protect the girl.
And of course, I
acknowledged your wish.
However, I never said I would
fight abiding by your wishes.
In a battle, the top priority
is to achieve victory.
And to do that, I'll resort
to any means necessary.
-You've already aimed
for Tokiko twice.
I also will resort to any
means, no matter what it takes!
NEGORO: Here I come.
-Bring it on.
The next time you show
yourself, you better
be ready for your defeat!
-Here I come.
Buso Renkin of Floating Mine.
Here comes a Bubble Cage!
The Bubble Cage
increases in number
as it explodes and pressures
the space to restrict you.
Your turn, Inukai!
-All right.
Let's go.
Buso Renkin of Military
Dog, Killer Rabies.
-Sword Samurai X!
-Hey, that kid is pretty good.
-Not good enough.
MAN: Damn.
He's still going.
-It's too dangerous to continue.
Let's just retreat for now.
-It really won't
make any difference.
I think we should
go as far as we can.
-With this many people,
even Victor can't.
-Time to die.
Buso Renkin of Great Axe.
Fatal Attraction!
-Wha-- What is this?
-I can't stand.
-Is this gravity manipulation?
-All Alchemist
Warriors must die!
-Buso Renkin of Gas Mask.
Aerial Operator.
All of you.
Now's our chance.
Leave this place immediately.
Come on.
Let's go.
-We're saved.
-Very sneaky.
-Get out of here.
Hurry.
-Shisui.
Let's go.
-Hm.
They've fled.
-I knew it was the right
choice to bring you along
in the battle against Victor.
Without you, we could've
been completely annihilated.
-He's powerful.
It's impossible for normal
Warriors to fight against him.
-Yes, you're right.
That Buso Renkin with
gravity manipulation
is a serious threat, for sure.
But next time, we won't have
any trouble locating him
since this Buso Renkin
of Radar, Hermes Drive,
is now able to locate
Victor's signal.
-Are you really
sure it's this way?
You know there is no absolute
guarantee that Kazuki has even
reached Newton Apple Academy
for Girls at this point.
That Ikusabe was quite
strong, and the two
that were going after Kazuki
are probably the same.
It could be all over by now.
Kazuki could
already be defeated.
Huh?
Wah!
Oh no, Pappy, Pappy!
Are you all right?
-Fantastic!
-Pappy, Pappy, Pappy!
Is everything all right?
Huh?
[snoring]
-Uh.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): It seems
Gota caught on to something.
Motor Gear's
offensive power is one
of the weakest among
the Buso Renkin.
Gota's battle style is to
use creativity and strategy
to compensate for that.
When things click in Gota's
head, then he is very reliable.
Just the sword!
So then he--
NEGORO: How is it?
From this inaccessible
dimension,
I can attack you
without showing myself.
Considering how you cannot
attack me in return,
you're powerless.
And this is the secret
trail's path to victory.
I'll increase my speed.
-Gota!
-Motor Gear!
Skywalker Mode!
-It's pointless.
Your act of escaping
means you've already
fallen into my trap.
What awaits you at the
end of that weak hope
is an even more tragic death.
Just like Victor
Three, Kazuki Muto,
you're simply engaging
in a futile struggle.
-Don't compare me to that
super naive, optimistic guy.
I really don't care
if he lives or dies.
If Tokiko is safe, I
don't care about the rest.
As long as I can protect her.
-And if we both want to
protect the same thing,
I bet the two of
us can be allies.
Damn it.
Hey, peeping Tom ninja!
NEGORO: What, droopy eyes?
-Tell me, Do you have an ally?
-Hmph.
Ridiculous.
Even if I had one, they're
just plain useless.
I am fine on my
own, don't you see?
You may be very good
with your surroundings,
but your reflexes are slower
when you are in motion.
I got you!
-Motor Gears, fire now!
-What?
-You're quite persistent.
But my attack was more
effective than yours.
-Hope you're ready,
because my next move
will spell the end of you.
This piece from your scarf
is what gave you away.
Although you said that not
even a speck of dust can enter,
your clothes and your
gear are the exception.
The secret behind that
pathway is not noticeable
when you look at
it at first glance.
Your hair is woven
into the fabric.
Which means the scarf is
recognized as a part of you.
The key to the pathway's
passage is your body's DNA.
-Impressive you figured it out.
But unfortunately,
just knowing that,
you still can't get
into the pathway.
That's--
-My Motor Gear's completely
covered with your blood.
You're finished.
[scream]
-Just like you, I'm also
fine fighting on my own.
TOKIKO: Gota!
Where is he?
Did you defeat him?
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): Since we
want to protect the same thing,
I guess for now--
-It was an easy victory.
I bet that fool Kazuki is
all alone and helpless.
So let's hurry up and find him.
[heavy breathing]
-Where are they?
I really hope they're
both all right.
What's that?
Captain Bravo?
-It's time to settle
our score, Kazuki Muto.
[theme music]
TOKIKO: The time has
come to settle things
between two men who
share the same belief.
Protecting the things most
important each of them
will thrust them into
a decisive battle.
Next time, With
Strength and Feeling.
I'll splatter your guts!