NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
-Do you swear to live
together for all eternity?
-Yes!
Yes mommy, I do!
-How about you, Shu?
-Yes, I do.
-All right, then!
Mommy's going to sweat too!
Not just the two of you,
but the three of us.
SHUSUI: The
childhood game that I
remember the most is the wedding
game that my sister loved
so much.
WOMAN: OK, kids.
It's time to go to bed now.
OUKA: Why, Mommy?
I wanna play it again!
SHUSUI: It always ended with
the three of us together.
WOMAN: Yes, honey.
We will.
We'll do it when we
wake up tomorrow.
SHUSUI: I didn't
really understand
the meaning of the pledge,
but my mom and my sister
seemed happy, so I
was happy as well.
And I really didn't understand
'til death do us part either.
That's why I had no idea
what happened to my mom
that morning.
We didn't have a dad.
We didn't know why.
I didn't understand.
My sister, my mom,
and I. Our world
consisted of the three of us
in a one bedroom apartment.
-It's dangerous outside,
so don't go out.
-OK!
SHUSUI: Mom always
left for work early
and came back late at night.
We listened to what
Mom said and never left
the room in her absence.
Not once did we ever take
a single step outside.
As time went by,
we began to grow
like we were in
some kind of race.
But for some reason, Mom
became smaller and thinner.
And then, one morning, Mom
stopped moving altogether.
-Mommy, wake up!
It's morning!
Come on.
Wake up, Mommy!
SHUSUI: We waited.
And even though we waited for a
long time, Mom didn't wake up.
We grew impatient, so we went
against our mother's words,
and eventually, we
decided to go outside.
-Come on, Ouka.
Let's go outside.
-But Mommy said
outside is dangerous.
SHUSUI: However--
[gasping]
SHUSUI AND OUKA: Open the door!
Open, please!
Open the door!
Help!
Open!
Open up!
Open the door!
SHUSUI: We cried out for help.
We yelled at the top of our lung
so that someone could hear us.
-That apartment is so loud!
It is kind of
disturbing, isn't it?
-I think we should just
mind out own business
and not get involved.
-Shut up, you little brats.
Be quiet in there, will you?
SHUSUI: But no one heard us.
No.
It wasn't that no one heard us.
It was that no one
wanted to listen.
We lost track of time.
Then one day, without
any kind of warning,
we were taken under
police custody.
-No, I really didn't
notice anything at all.
-Since it was always
so quiet, I had
no idea there were kids inside.
SHUSUI: It turned
out, the woman we
thought was our mother
had kidnapped us
from our real parents
after an emotional affair,
kept us locked
up, and raised us.
Our real parents
refused to take us in.
There was no other
place for us to go.
We snuck out of the
hospital in order
to make sure that we
wouldn't get separated.
So, um, where do
you want to go now?
-Anywhere is fine, but
you have to promise
to stay with me, Shusui.
Kay?
-Ouka.
-We'll be together forever, K?
'Til death do us part.
-Give me your money!
And all your food!
Hand over some medication, now!
-Well, well, well!
What a cute little mugger!
DR. BUTTERFLY: Ah.
Those eyes.
They're starting
to muddle nicely.
-You see?
What did I tell you?
Something good always happens
during a walk in the moonlight.
This little one is
definitely a good catch.
-Come along, boy.
From what I can
tell, you probably
don't have a place to go anyway.
-No, I won't!
Not without my sister!
I won't go anywhere without her!
-A sister, you say?
I don't mind.
Bring her along.
However, if she doesn't
have eyes like yours,
it's going to be hard
for her to survive.
-At some point, the LXE
adopted dozens of kids
to serve as Familiars,
but only a handful
were able to
survive to this day.
All the rest failed
and were devoured.
We're part of that
lucky few that survived.
-Shusui, Ouka.
I don't know what to say.
-We don't want revenge.
We don't blame
anyone for anything.
And our aim isn't to destroy
or rule the world in any way,
either.
Actually, this world
has no meaning to us.
We just really
don't care for it.
This entire time, we
had just one wish.
To become Homunculi.
We want a life where even
death can't separate us.
So we can live forever
in a world of our own.
-Is that all you have to say?
The two of you may think
you've had a hard life.
That's unfortunate for you.
But a Homunculus eats humans,
and I can't allow you two
to become Homunculi and inflict
pain and suffering on others.
So why don't you two
be together in death?
-No, Tokiko, wait!
-Kazuki.
What are you doing?
-Me?
Look at yourself, Tokiko.
How can you do this?
They're still
humans, aren't they?
So how can you tell them to die?
-They are the enemy who've sold
their souls to the Homunculi.
All Homunculi must die!
They must be eliminated!
-Stop it!
They're still human beings.
It's not too late for them yet.
They could start over.
The last time, I know I
failed trying to save Chouno,
but this time I--
this time I will!
-So, are you telling me that you
are going to protect the enemy?
-Look at them.
In their current condition,
they pose no threat.
In any case, I don't want
to kill unnecessarily.
And honestly, Tokiko, I
don't want you to either.
-Kazuki.
You're just one big dilemma.
Your kindness becomes your
liability during a fight,
and I'm afraid that one
day, that liability's
going to get you killed.
So before that
happens, I'm gonna
take away your means to fight.
I'm sorry, Kazuki, but I'm
taking away your fighting
strength and putting an end
to your life as a Warrior!
-No, Tokiko.
Please, don't!
-Ouka, are you all right?
Ouka.
-I'm fine.
But I guess, either
way, it's over, Shusui.
We've failed our mission.
Now either we get
eaten by the Homunculi,
or get killed by an
Alchemist Warrior.
We've already lost.
-Huh?
-Move aside!
I can't believe you
didn't run away.
-Why?
Our fate is already sealed.
-That's very commendable of you.
Kazuki!
I told you.
You can't kill them.
Don't you see?
They're still human beings.
-You don't understand.
They are allied
with the Homunculi.
Can't you see that?
Who do you want to save
in the end, your sister
and friends, or these two?
Tell me, Kazuki.
-All of them.
I want to protect every
single one of them!
-Stop fooling around, and
make a choice, will you?
-I can't!
I'm not going to choose
who lives and who dies.
I'm always going to
save every life I can.
I owe it to you.
Tokiko, that the first night
when we met, you gave me life.
You even gave up a precious
Kakugane to save my life.
And because you saved
my life, I didn't
have to be separated from
Mahiro or my friends.
And I also got to
know you, Tokiko.
Perhaps that night, it
also meant a new beginning
for the twins.
Maybe we're meant to help them.
To end their world of
loneliness and start a new life.
And that is why you
can't end their lives
like it doesn't matter.
[groan]
-I want to become as
powerful as I possibly can.
The stronger I become, the
closer we get to our wish.
Ha!
SHUSUI (VOICEOVER): I'll win.
I can't lose!
Not here.
Not now!
-Kazuki!
-Huh?
Ouka.
Ouka!
Why-- did you do that?
-I thought back then,
when the door was locked
in that apartment,
when we were little,
and we were screaming,
asking for help,
trying to get
out-- if Kazuki had
been right outside, or
nearby, I have no doubt
he would have come
in and saved us.
I'm sure of it.
I tought, he might have
become our good friend.
And I imagined a better
life, we would have never
lost our faith in people.
'Til death do us
part, and I guess
that time has finally come.
Goodbye, my Shusui.
Thanks for everything
that you've done.
-No, not yet!
Don't give up, Ouka!
The Kakugane.
The healing power of the
Kakugane can save her.
-It's no use.
The bleeding won't stop.
-You mean two of them
still aren't enough?
Tokiko.
In the condition
that I'm in, there's
no way I can remove the
Kakugane from my body.
Tokiko, the choice is yours.
You can either save
her, or let her die.
-My choice, huh?
But when I asked you to
choose just a minute ago,
you didn't even bother.
[gulp]
-Fine.
Unlike you, I am going
to make a choice.
Buso Renkin, deactivate.
-Thank you, Tokiko.
-Yeah, whatever.
And if that doesn't
help, then too bad.
KAZUKI: Al right.
The bleeding stopped.
Good.
We can save her
-In times of sickness,
and in health.
-In joy, and in sorrow.
SHUSUI: For richer.
OUKA: Or for poorer.
SHUSUI: To love--
OUKA: And cherish.
YOUNG SUSHUI AND
OUKA (VOICEOVER):
To comfort and
protect, from this day
forward, 'til death do us part.
Will you promise to
live together forever?
PAPILLON: How touching.
I'm so glad you didn't have
to go through a situation
like you did last time.
But it might be a different
story for those twins.
You know, even if a new
world is opened up for them,
they have already experienced
the dark world of alchemy
far too deeply.
MOONFACE: And
that's not something
you can leave behind so easily.
-Mm?
-Moon.
Life can be so ephemeral.
Moon!
-What are you doing here?
Being their watcher is my duty.
-Taking a stroll
in the moonlight.
But you know something?
I was actually curious
about that infamous Warrior.
The one that defeated you
when you became a Homunculus.
But frankly, I'm
not very impressed.
Now come on, don't
scowl like that.
Give me a smile.
Aw.
I have no intention of getting
involved with your enemy,
but I'll admit I'm
planning to make
those two failures my dinner.
Come to think of it, on
the night we found them,
it was a full moon,
like this one.
I thought they had such promise.
I really did.
Oh?
-Comet Bravo Kick.
BRAVO AND MOONFACE:
Bizarre looking.
-I see.
So you are the third one.
And I bet you're
also the leader.
Am I right?
-If you plan to lay your
hands on those children,
you're gonna have
to deal with me.
-With pleasure.
But as much as I'd like
to, unfortunately I've
been told by Dr. Butterfly
to restrain myself.
It's a shame, but I guess
I should follow orders.
What's your name?
-Captain Bravo.
-Moon.
What a magnificent name.
My name is Moonface.
I'm sure we'll meet
in battle soon enough.
Moon!
-Yes.
I'm sure we will.
The other one has left, as well.
BOY: It's been 10 days since
the Hayasaka twins were in a car
accident, and we're
just finding out
where they've been hospitalized?
-Let's go visit them!
-Car accident?
-Don't ask.
That's outside of
my jurisdiction.
Those twins have now been placed
in the custody of the Warrior
Chief.
I wonder how much information
he was able to get from them?
-It's good he's got it covered.
I just really hope
they're getting better.
-Only authorized persons
are allowed to visit.
-What does that really mean?
I wonder if we need to be
family members to be let in?
-What exactly is our
relationship to them, anyway?
-Well, we're just classmates.
-Not true!
We've already compared
sizes with them, remember?
That makes us practically
family, don't you think?
-What the hell were
you guys doing?
MAHIRO: Well, in that case,
we're just as qualified.
-You compared sizes, too?
-Most definitely!
-In that case, get ready!
Let's go for it!
Charge!
[shouting]
-What the hell are you doing?
If you fool around
with medical personnel,
get ready to pay the price.
-When it comes to your health,
remember that we doctors always
know what is best.
-We can take on a bunch
of junk food punks.
-We're ready, so bring it on.
-What is wrong
with this hospital?
-Hey, Kazuki!
Catch this!
-Got it!
-Kazuki, this too!
-What?
-Hello, Mr. Bravo.
So are you here
for another visit?
-Yes.
Thank you for everything.
DOCTOR: Quick!
Those two are getting away!
-Hey, there!
No running in the hallways.
This hospital has connections
with headquarters.
They accommodate our
needs well, and we
have a little freedom here.
[knocking]
-Ouka?
We're coming in.
-Hey there, Bravo, my buddy!
Now, don't you get tired
of coming every day?
Oh!
You're here too, Kazuki?
Great.
-Ouka can't hold long
conversations yet,
so I'm interrogating her by
leaving Angel Gozen's speaking
ability turned on.
-Yup!
-Wow.
It's a talking Buso Renkin.
-A pretty stupid
one, if you ask me.
-Mm?
What was that?
Oh, lookie here, scarface
calling me stupid.
Well, what's your
weapon, a Valkyrie Skirt?
Ha!
So which part is the
death scythe, huh?
No!
Please!
Help, help!
TOKIKO: I'm actually
curious about its AI.
Can I take it apart?
BRAVO: I was pretty
curious about that, myself.
Let's see.
Bravo Arts 1 of 13,
all-seeing Bravo Eye.
I got it.
-Amazing.
Is that another
ability of Silver Skin?
-Negative!
This sight is a result
of intense training.
It seems like Ouka and Gozen
share their consciousness.
In other words, Gozen is
a part of Ouka Hayasaka.
-So what is he hiding
behind that smile?
-Hey, by the way, Ouka--
where did Shusui go?
-Shusui Hayasaka was already
discharged this morning.
So then, you want to go
into training right away?
-Yes.
I'm going back to training
with a swordmaster
I've trained with before.
-Tell me, are you trying
to become stronger
in order to defeat Kazuki?
-No.
The one I wish to
overcome is myself.
-Very well.
But I need to
confiscate the Kakugane.
And also, I need you to promise
that you will contact us once
a week.
-Dear Ouka--
I understand.
Take care of yourself.
-I'm sorry.
But I promise I will come back.
-Up until now, we had pledged to
live together forever and ever.
But we were just
clinging to each other.
We closed ourselves off
in our own little world,
and were afraid one day
we had to part in death.
From now then, we're going
to stand on our own two feet.
I'll walk on my own, and
I will live on my own.
Then we both live
in the real world.
BRAVO: This is for you.
From Shusui.
-Ah!
I thought something smelled
really good. is it melon?
-Oh, I almost forgot.
Here you go.
Enjoy.
-Huh?
Ah!
Ah, this is covered with blood!
-And these flowers
are for you, Ouka.
From Mahiro and the others.
-They smell really nice.
-Everyone was very
worried about you.
When you get better,
we should all
get together and hang
out, or something.
This truly is a new beginning.
You don't have to
be alone anymore.
-They-- they really
do smell wonderful.
I wish I could share them with
Shusui right now, you know?
-Are those flowers I smell?
Must be my imagination.
But in any case, they
sure did smell nice.
[theme music]
TOKIKO: It was a
campus covered in fog.
Students screaming echoed in
front of countless monsters,
in order not to make any
other sacrifices like before.
Run, Kazuki!
Next episode, Carnival.
I'll splatter your guts!
-Hi!
This is Mahiro Muto, once again
introducing the Buso Renkin
so everyone can understand.
Our fourth presentation is
the Angel Gozen and the Sword
Samurai X. They're
beautiful, handsome, smart,
and also athletically
outstanding.
No matter how you look at
them, the twin siblings Ouka
and Shusui Hayasaka
are just perfect.
But the two were LXE Familiars.
There they each
received a Kakugane,
which gave them the
power of Buso Renkin.
For Ouka, Angel Gozen.
And for Shusui, the Sword
Samurai X. Angel Gozen's
distinctive characteristic
is the cutesy ugly automaton
Angel Gozen.
Angel Gozen shares its
consciousness with Ouka,
and seems busy being angry
and crying all the time.
But that is supposed
to be just another side
of Ouka's personality.
Tokiko thinks it's a
true reflection of Ouka,
because that woman
is dark hearted.
Oh, and another thing.
When attacking, Angel Gozen
uses Ouka's bow and arrow
to create high speed shots.
That's right.
It is perfectly capable
of attacking, as well.
Ouka can transfer physical
changes to herself
by shooting others
with her arrow.
She used this ability
to save my big brother.
Oh, this must have
really hurt, I'm sure.
-Oh!
And it turned out Ouka
is a really nice person.
Oh, I just knew she was.
Now, moving on to Shusui.
He's the one who gave my
big brother a tough battle.
His Buso Renkin is
Sword Samurai X.
Because Shusui is
a master of kendo,
he must have the
strength of Samson
to wield a Japanese katana.
But the Sword Samurai X also
has the special property
to neutralize energy
based attacks.
The blade absorbs the
energy, and releases it
from the bottom
cord, which means
all of Kazuki's energy based
attacks with the Sunlight Heart
are absorbed, and therefore
have no effect on Shusui.
Kazuki himself
thought he was done
for when he was faced
with a special property.
Ouka and Shusui have
been through a lot,
but thanks to
Kazuki's kind heart,
they've changed their ways,
and now the both of them
are our friends!
We even compared
each others' sizes,
so we have an unbreakable bond.
I would love for all of us
to hang out together sometime
again.
Okie dokie, tune in next time!