NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the kakugane.
This device activates upon
a person's fighting instinct
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form creating
a weapon like no other.
It's name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
-I'm sorry, Tokiko.
-Kazuki!
Kazuki.
-The two Victors have
indeed disappeared
from the face of the earth and
the crisis is now finally over.
But this-- this is--
[laughing]
-That's just the way it is.
That's absurdity for you.
After all, that's
how the world is.
That's how it's been, and
how it will always be.
-You don't really mean
what you're saying.
I understand the
outcome is upsetting.
However, results are results.
No matter how much
sorrow there may be,
people's lives will continue
on as if nothing ever happened.
No matter how great
the sorrow may be.
Yet, I believe
everything happened
the way it was supposed to.
-But--
-Rather than dwelling on
the current circumstances,
we must focus on
where to go from here.
That is the duty for
those of us left behind.
-It's not like you
had to tell me that.
-The aftermath
clean up has begun.
The two of you are going to
have a little more work ahead.
-All right, let's go.
-Yes, sir.
GOTA (VOICEOVER): Tokiko.
-Hey, where should
we go to next?
-Who wants to go
for another drink?
-You're so dirty.
-Hey, taxi.
Taxi.
Stop, you jerk, stop!
-How boring.
There's absolutely
nothing here for me.
A world without
Kazuki Muto around
is a dull, pointless,
boring place.
Kazuki Muto.
-Hey, come on, Tokiko, it's
time we all go back to school.
Everyone understands.
Nobody will say
anything, I promise.
-You have to face reality,
Kazuki's gone now.
-I know.
That's why I've been thinking.
I've been thinking about
what I can do for Kazuki one
last time before
leaving this city.
-Has she been like that
this whole time, Ouka.
-Yes, it's a sign that she's
starting to recover though.
She didn't even speak
at all until today.
-I don't blame her after going
through something like that.
Her physical wounds
will eventually heal,
but her wounded heart
might take awhile.
-Tokiko.
-Regardless of the facts,
we can't just give up.
-Kazuki would say the same
thing if he were here.
-Kazuki isn't here anymore.
However, there's got to be
something that we can still do.
-Yes.
-Wher-- I didn't even know
what to say to her just now.
-It's just as well.
Right now there are
probably no words
that can reach her anyway.
-I know, but still.
-No matter what you say,
it will just hurt her.
All we can do now
is watch over her.
Weren't you the one who
said that once, Bravo?
I'm pretty sure she'll be OK.
I have no doubt she'll be able
to find an answer on her own.
Don't worry.
After all, she was one
of your subordinates,
so I'm sure she'll be OK.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Kazuki saved this world.
Kazuki protected this city with
his own life, but even so, I--
-Tokiko.
-Kazuki.
What am I supposed to do?
Kazuki!
-I'm a little worried.
Mahiro hasn't been the
same at all since that day,
and Tokiko hasn't
come to school either.
I wonder how she's doing?
-Damn it.
What the hell was that?
-The harsh truth is
we are outsiders.
If Bravo hadn't told
us what happened,
we would've still
been kept in the dark.
Shouldn't we accept things
as is and stop wondering?
-But Rokumasu.
-But he gave his life to
protect this world, and yet--
-Isn't that usually
how it is anyway?
The majority of
people everywhere just
continue going about
their lives unaware
that something significant
has happened to this world.
That's the way it is, and that's
the way it will always be.
-Stop talking like you
know it all, will ya?
-Kazuki.
-Damn it.
You idiot!
-Yah!
-You shouldn't abuse
your body too much.
-Next.
Ahhhhh!
-Tokiko.
What's going on?
What have you been doing?
Fighting SIM battles
this whole time?
You have, haven't you?
Honestly, you've just recovery.
You shouldn't be pushing
yourself like this.
Tokiko, take care of yourself.
-N-- Next.
-Tokiko.
Tokiko.
To be honest, I can't
stand seeing you like this.
Please, cheer up.
Whatever it takes,
I'll do anything just
to see smile again.
Tokiko.
-Thanks, Gota, but--
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Kazuki.
What can I do for you?
-Eventually, I'll settle things
with you once and for all.
Until I do, I won't be able to
be myself and truly take off.
-Chouno.
I also plan to settle things
with you once and for all.
-I will settle it.
-How are the missions
in other areas going?
-50% are complete.
The rest are in progress.
We are currently
working on bringing
every confirmed homunculi
under our control.
-Followed by a
gradual suspension
of all alchemist army activity?
Are you serious about that?
-Yes.
I've been having meetings with
armies from various nations.
It's been thousands of
years since alchemy began
and the completion of
the philosopher's stone
is still far away.
In addition, we've not been
able to properly utilize
the power we currently have and
we continue to make mistakes.
I believe it is time for us to
take a step back and reexamine
our progress thus far.
-Is that even
possible right now?
-Whether it's possible
or not, it must be done.
It's the least we
can do for those
two warriors up on the moon.
-Great Warrior Chief.
-Warrior Tokiko, what is it?
-Great Warrior Chief,
I have a request.
-Tokiko, I heard.
I know about your final mission
to take care of Papillon.
You can count me in.
-Hey, come on, you
guys are so slow.
What the heck took you so long?
I was getting tired of waiting.
-We heard about what you
guys are planning to do.
-And we won't let
you do this alone.
-That's right, Tokiko.
We were getting a little
worry too, you know.
I mean, why take off
without even saying a word?
Think about it.
That's not very nice.
-Geez, how come you're
so well-informed?
-You really shouldn't
underestimate
my extremely efficient
intelligence network.
-Tokiko, your orders.
-Tokiko.
-All right, let's go
to our final mission.
-Tokiko.
Hey, Tokiko.
-We are now in enemy territory.
We must not let our guard down.
-I'm aware of that.
Let's go.
-Hm, if you're going to watch
the moon, do it someplace else.
And if you're going to
eat, eat somewhere else.
-Want some?
It's my Mama.
Well, actually, it's the
remains of her failed attempt
to clone herself.
-It doesn't even
wet my appetite.
-Strange that you say that.
This has been my main diet
for close to 100 years.
I'd heard that you didn't have
any urges for cannibalism.
I guess it's true then huh?
The reason a homunculus
has the urge to eat humans,
some researchers
say it's attributed
to an instinctive attachment.
In other words,
it's like a desire
to regain the human elements
that it had originally lost.
You don't have any
attachments to human elements,
to the human world,
or to society.
As a homunculus
you are incomplete,
but you've accomplished
what other homunculi haven't
been able to do, breaking
away from being human.
You are something
completely new that's
neither human nor homunculus.
You might literally
be a superhuman.
-Go and speak your
nonsense someplace else.
-You're right.
This conversation is probably
nonsense to you and me,
but I will tell you something
relevant for your own good.
The alchemist warriors
are already nearby.
Or did you know that already?
-That's none of your concern.
I have prepared an appropriate
welcome for unwanted visitors.
-Long time no see.
-You really did it, didn't you?
-The time has come for revenge.
-Don't even think you're
going to get past here.
-Animal type homunculike
created by Papillon.
-Did he recreate them with
Dr. Alexandria's cloning
technology?
-That confirms it.
There's no doubt Papillon
was on the other side.
Let's go.
-Buso renkin of archery.
-Buso renkin of Katana sword.
Sword Samurai X.
-Buso renkin of
chakram, motor gear.
-So who's my opponent, huh?
Come on.
-Out of my way.
-You won't get through.
-Clones.
-Go on ahead, Tokiko.
-I don't think so.
-Tokiko, go ahead.
-So what do you want?
Are you on a mission
to eliminate me?
-No, Papillon,
I've come to settle
things in Kazuki's place.
-No one could ever
take his place.
Are you saying Kazuki
Muto is replaceable?
[theme music]
-Will my heart and
soul reach you?
I want to live with you forever.
Kazuki, thank you.
Next time, the series
finale, "Period."