NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the possessor's
inner power into tangible form,
creating a weapon like no other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: An obscure antidote
is the only hope for Tokiko
to remove the parasite
Homunculus nesting in her body.
Kazuki goes to find
Chouno, the only person who
can provide this, but Kazuki
has sustained serious injuries,
and his stamina
has been drained.
To assist his healing
process, Tokiko
entrusts him with
her own Kakugane.
-I'll be back, Tokiko.
Everyone, just wait for me.
[heavy breathing]
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): This
must be Chouno's house.
What you mean, you don't know?
-It's been a long
time, and I don't
care to know of his whereabouts.
-But that's--
-It was my intention
that he would eventually
inherit the Chouno
family fortune.
I gave him every
conceivable kind
of education for the gifted, and
it all seemed to be paying off.
People around us
would speak of how
he was following
in the footsteps
of his great, great
grandfather, who
laid the foundation
for this family.
But now look at him.
A 19-year-old recluse who
repeats the same year twice.
-Chouno!
-What do you want
with Master Jiro?
-J-Jiro?
-Big brother is missing, huh?
How amusing.
-Chouno's younger brother?
-If you find him,
give him this message.
It has been decided that
Jiro will be the family's
sole successor, and that he
is no longer needed here.
-Are you serious?
Your Chouno's
father, aren't you?
He's suffering from
a terrible disease.
-What of it?
If he isn't able to
carry out his purpose,
then he is of no use to me.
MAN: Get lost, kid.
[phone ringing]
MAHIRO: Yes, hello?
Oh, hi Kazuki.
Tokiko?
Yeah!
Oh, don't worry.
She's just fine.
I swear by nightingale,
I, nurse Mahiro,
will make sure to
look after her.
DAIHAMA: Is that her own outfit?
OKAKURA: Don't tell me she
has a thing for uniforms.
ROKUMASU: Well, the
truth is, you're
more like a caretaker
than an actual nurse.
-Stop interrupting, or I'm
gonna give all you guys shots!
-So Chouno didn't go to
his family home, huh?
Well, do you think
there's a possibility
that his father might be lying?
KAZUKI (ON PHONE): Not a chance.
If I were Chouno, there's no
way I'd go back there either.
He clearly isn't
welcome there at all.
-Then that means the only place
that he would return to is
where it all began for him.
It's gotta be.
-Got it.
I'll keep looking.
TOKIKO: Stop running.
If you overdo it, you'll
collapse for sure this time.
-I'm fine.
So far
TOKIKO: So far?
-Only three and a
half hours left.
Come to think of it, I haven't
eaten anything since yesterday.
Once I've become a
Homunculus, I'll have to eat.
I wonder what would be good?
I guess it'll have to be humans?
-I've finally found you, Chouno.
-Ah, yes.
You're Muto.
-Chouno!
-Muto!
TOKIKO: What's wrong, Kazuki?
What was that loud
noise just now?
Did you get excited and
collapse, or something?
You're kidding me.
Didn't I warn you?
-You look so energetic
all of a sudden.
-I found him, Tokiko.
Just as you predicted.
His source of emotional
support is the alchemy research
his great, great
grandfather left behind.
His last resort
was the warehouse
where he discovered
that research.
-Then Washio must've
been defeated.
Otherwise you wouldn't be alive.
-That's right.
And he was worried
about you right up
until he took his last breath.
-So what?
Who cares?
If he can't carry
out his function,
then he is of no use to me.
-The antidote and the
Homunculus embryo--
give them to me, Chouno.
-I'll give you the antidote.
But I can't give you this.
If I don't have this, I'll
soon die from this disease.
KAZUKI: I cannot let you
become a Homunculus like this.
I promised myself I wouldn't
allow anymore sacrifices.
TOKIKO: No use trying
to talk to him, Kazuki.
He won't listen to
anyone right now.
Grab the Homunculus embryo
and get out of there quickly.
It's an incomplete embryo.
Once you remove it from
the cultivation solution,
it'll die right away.
Got it, Tokiko.
But I've got one last
thing to tell him.
-Huh?
-Chouno.
Listen to me.
Whether you become a
Homunculus or remain human,
if you continue the
way you are, you're
going to be by yourself forever
and you'll die all alone.
Even if you have a grave,
there'll be no flowers.
Nothing.
-Do you think I care?
-No one will even remember you.
-I don't care what
happens after I die.
-Listen.
All you have to do is
make amends to those
you've sacrificed and I'll--
-You'll what?
-Yes.
You'll what?
Please tell us.
However he dies is really
none of your business.
You are quite a
hypocrite, I see.
-Just what do you want, Jiro?
-Well, well.
You still haven't given
him my father's message.
Then allow me.
I've officially been named
the family successor.
All inheritance will go to me.
-Oh, is that what it is?
That really doesn't
matter to me anymore.
-No kidding.
Really?
Well, I just want
you to know it does
make a huge difference to me.
Even though I was
born into this family,
I was always treated
second rate just
because I was born
a year after you.
Ordinary education, ordinary
life, ordinary name.
I wasn't granted
the suffix shaku,
which carries the pride of
our great great grandfather.
Jiro, the second born.
Until you got sick, I was
nothing more than a worm,
crawling on the ground.
-Well then.
You must be satisfied now.
-And that's the reason I
can't have you recovering
from your illness, big brother.
I didn't really understand
the conversation,
but it seemed to me you'd be
saved if you had this, right?
-Don't you dare, you fool.
It only needs a little more
time before it's complete!
No!
JIRO: Nobody needs
a person like you.
-Don't you think it's funny
how twisted this family is?
JIRO: Die!
Hurry up and die!
-Idiots.
-So, are you dead yet?
-Come to me!
You and I are the same.
You should want to
live more than anyone.
More than anything!
So come.
Let us become a
Homunculus now, and be
reborn into a
magnificent Papillon!
-What happened?
What happened to you?
-Muto.
As I recall, you did say
you wouldn't allow any more
sacrifices, didn't you?
Well, too bad.
Ooh.
As black as the devil himself,
and as scorching as all hell.
Almost as sweet as a kiss.
So this is what
humans taste like.
TOKIKO (ON PHONE):
What's going on, Kazuki?
Did something happen?
-Now I am complete.
Papillon!
-You pervert!
-You mean perfect.
I have achieved a
complete transformation.
Mm.
It does hurt a bit.
Ooh.
Ah.
But it's good.
-Look at that.
It's-- It's-- It's a monster!
-Not a monster.
A superhuman!
TOKIKO (ON PHONE):
Gunshots and screams.
Chouno has become a humanoid
Homunculus, hasn't he?
KAZUKI (ON PHONE): I'm sorry.
-It's not your fault at all.
Get out as soon as possible.
Just as humans and
monkeys are nothing alike,
humanoid and animal Homunculi
are completely different.
He's not an opponent you
can take on right now.
Kazuki!
-I know.
But I still haven't
gotten the antidote.
TOKIKO (ON PHONE):
Just forget it, Kazuki.
-Buso Renkin!
What?
-Ha ha.
-My Buso Renkin.
It won't activate.
-The game is over.
[gurgling]
-Oh.
This body really uses
up a lot of energy.
I guess I'll have to
get some food first.
Almost midnight.
Three hours left until that
girl turns into a Homunculus.
You just lie there,
grief stricken
by your own helplessness.
-Jiro, sir.
-Aren't you cold, sir?
-Jiro, eh?
Hm.
Well, I guess we do look alike.
-Hm?
Hey.
Did you just hear something
coming from the front porch?
-You're imagining things.
-I know.
Anyone who can tell me
apart from Jiro lives.
That's fun.
-Let's check it out.
-Whatever.
-Now let's see.
I wonder how many
will figure it out.
MAN: Jiro, sir--
MAN: Please don't
scare us like that.
[gurgling]
TOKIKO (ON PHONE): Kazuki?
Kazuki.
Answer me.
Kazuki?
Do you hear me?
Kazuki!
Answer me.
KAZUKI (ON PHONE):
I can hear you.
Tokiko.
-Thank goodness you woke up.
You must get out
of there right now.
-I can still fight.
TOKIKO (ON PHONE): Impossible.
You're only starting to
because of healing effects
of the Kakugane.
Wait until the next
Warrior years you got it?
-But what about the antidote?
There won't be time.
TOKIKO (ON PHONE):
Enough already.
You've done more than enough.
It's OK.
I've accepted my fate.
Just get back here quick.
Everyone's waiting for you.
-Do me a favor.
Please put Mahiro and
the others on the phone.
-I peeled some apples for you.
Strawberry talk
temporarily suspended.
-Hey Kazuki.
Calling for a back up after all!
All right!
I'm ready to show you the
true power of Okakura.
-Right.
I want to see it.
-Um.
Kazuki.
That copy of "Erotic
Ladies Maximum"
you had under your pillow.
I've hidden it somewhere else.
You'll have to be
more careful, man.
If Tokiko or Mahiro find it,
they might get upset or angry.
-Thanks for saving me, Daihama.
-Just a warning for you.
When you return, come
through the back.
The dorm adviser's really
got his eyes out for you,
so you had better be careful.
-Right.
If push comes to shove,
Answer at roll call for me.
MAHIRO (ON PHONE):
Hey big brother.
Tokiko is doing fine.
Leave her to me.
I'm taking good care of her.
We're all having
apples right now,
but if you don't
come back quickly,
there aren't gonna
be any left for you.
-Well, just save some for me.
I can't go back
right away, but--
-Kazuki.
KAZUKI (ON PHONE): Tokiko.
I'm OK.
Hearing everyone's voices.
I feel like it really
gave me some strength.
I'll get the antidote
and be back for sure.
Just trust me.
Listen, Tokiko.
I'll be borrowing
some of your power.
[crashing]
[shouting]
[gunshots]
-Not a single one.
-What's going on out there?
What's all the commotion?
Hm?
Hmph.
-Father.
-Huh?
Whoa, what a fantastic costume.
What party are you
going to tonight, Jiro?
-That's right.
It's a memorial in memory of the
dear, deceased Koushaku Chouno.
-Jiro.
-I get it now.
Koushaku Chouno
didn't die tonight.
He's been dead for
a long time already.
Now it's time for the
after party to begin!
Let's celebrate the birth
of the Homunculus Papillon!
Since this world doesn't
need Koushaku Chouno,
I'll set his legacy all
on fire and burn it down.
I'll light a bonfire befitting
of this icy dark night.
A magnificent bonfire!
KAZUKI: I won't let
you do such a thing.
-You, huh?
Now, I told you to
give into your despair.
-Chouno!
-Yes?
-My Kakugane.
-Listen, Tokiko.
I'll be borrowing
some of your power.
Double Buso Renkin!
Time to settle this.
-Come on.
-So, your wounds
have healed, huh?
-Double tomahawk?
No.
Double lance, huh?
Nice.
But are you able to
use it skillfully?
Covered with wounds, exhausted.
Your precious
double lance appears
unstable it looks like
it's going to fall apart.
You think you could
beat me like that?
Don't make me laugh.
[coughing]
TOKIKO (ON PHONE): Kazuki.
What was that awful
sound I just heard?
-Chouno just coughed up blood.
TOKIKO (ON PHONE): Does
Chouno have an emblem mark?
-Actually, I don't
see one anywhere.
TOKIKO (ON PHONE): I see.
Kazuki.
No, Chouno.
Listen carefully.
Your transformation
was unsuccessful.
Using an embryo
before completion
caused something to go wrong.
You turned into a
Homunculus, but you still
retained your diseased body.
With an immortal
and diseased body,
you'll continue to
experience pain and suffering
indefinitely.
That's the price
you're going to have
to pay for attempting
to lengthen your life,
while sacrificing the
lives of so many others.
-My transformation
may have failed,
but it looks like I may
have another chance.
Since I've got one more
life standing in front of me
right now.
The antidote is in the box
hidden behind the incubator.
It'll explode instantly
if you force it
with anything other
than this key.
Now come and get it.
Time to eat you and
get the Kakugane!
Then when the woman
transforms and joins me,
I'll burn down this
world to ashes!
Ha ha ha!
-Not if I can help it!
I'm going to stop
you once and for all.
-Kazuki!
-This will be the final blow!
-The Kakugane is mine!
[shout]
-Impossible.
I may not be complete, but
I'm still a superhuman.
How could a mere
humans like you--
-I may be just a human,
but unlike you, I've
already fought many
life and death battles.
-So you're stronger and
you defeated me, but now
what are you going to do?
I've become a
Homunculus, which means
I won't stop eating
human beings.
Not to mention the fact that
the key to that woman's antidote
is in this stomach.
Will you wait for it to
come out with my excrement?
Come on, what will
you do with me now?
What will you do?
-Forgive me, Koushaku Chouno!
PAPILLON: Ah.
My name.
-Don't apologize, you hypocrite!
-The-- the key!
The key.
Tokiko.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): Light.
The morning sun?
Morning?
-Kazuki.
Did you know that up close,
your Buso Renkin energy
is a beautiful bright
golden yellow color?
Similar to the rays of the sun.
It took me a little
while, but how
about we name your
lance Sunlight Heart?
What do you think?
-Tokiko.
-Kazuki.
Thank you very much.
Now the mission is complete.
[theme music]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): A
mysterious organization
begins to make their move.
This is the true power of
the humanoid Homunculus.
A new battle begins.
Next time, whether or
not you're a hypocrite,
I'll splatter your guts!