[music playing]
NARRATOR: Caught in a
battle between a monster
and an Alchemist
Warrior, Kazuki Muto
instantly lost his
life when his heart
was pierced by an
evil homunculus.
-This wasn't supposed to happen.
NARRATOR: An Alchemist Warrior
named Tokiko gives Kazuki
a new life by replacing his
heart with the Kakugane,
an alloy activated by the
user's instinct to survive.
And now Kazuki must
choose his destiny.
-What you decide now will
determine your future.
Return to the world you know
or enter a world of battle.
I don't need to tell
you which world it
is you belong to, right?
NARRATOR: Instead, eager
by his impulse to help,
Kazuki makes the choice
to activate his new power.
-Hyaa!
Hyaa!
Huh?
TOKIKO: What about
your little sister?
-Don't worry about her.
She's safe and sound at home.
I ran full speed for 30 minutes,
but I still got lots of energy.
-It doesn't look that way.
Why did you come?
I warned you not to come here.
-I couldn't choose.
Mahiro's important to me, but--
NARRATOR: Kazuki has
not only acquired
a new power but a
new life as well.
He chooses to join
the warrior Tokiko
and to battle the homunculi.
[MUSIC - YOSHIKI FUKUYAMA,
"MAKKA NA CHIKAI"]
[clang]
MAN 1: Mita and Saruwatari?
MAN 2: Yes.
It seems the lab
has been destroyed
and we've also
lost communication
with the homunculi
that were hidden there.
MAN 1: An Alchemist Warrior, eh?
MAN 2: There can be
no other explanation.
[chuckling]
MAN 1: I see.
Then we must go and
introduce ourselves.
-What is this?
[grunt]
-Who's Tokiko Tsumura?
[scream]
-Kazkui has a girl's
name in his cell phone!
-No!
You're a nosy pervert!
-Did you hear that?
He said Okakura
was a nosy pervert.
-Well, Okakura is a pervert.
-Okakura the pervert?
-That's not true!
[screaming]
[sigh]
-That's what you get for looking
at somebody else's cell phone.
[phone ringing]
-Oh.
Tokiko, hi.
Yeah.
I'm still tired from last night.
It was kind of intense, but--
yeah, I'll be all right.
-Well, it doesn't sound like
an imaginary girlfriend.
-No fair.
He's laying on the
strawberry sweet talk.
-Strawberry.
-What could they
be talking about?
-They're meeting up together
at the haunted factory
right after school.
-You can hear him?
-Not really.
I was just able
to read his lips.
-Where the hell did
you pick up that skill?
TOKIKO: What are you doing?
-Hey, Tokiko.
-Let's go.
-All right.
I wonder if I did
the right thing
burying the bodies
of the victims who
were sacrificed last night.
-I don't see it as a bad
thing at all that you
paid your respects
to the departed.
-Yeah, I know, but
shouldn't we report this
to the police or something?
-That is not part
of my mission here.
My mission is to fight
and nothing else.
Besides, the police
can't solve this matter.
All they can do is
identify the bodies.
But that can't be done until
this whole thing is resolved.
The first thing we
have to do now is--
KAZUKI: Yeah, I've been
thinking about that too.
-Hmm?
-First of all, you have to give
my lance a really cool name.
Option number one,
"The Super Ultra
Special Strong Muscle Deluxe."
Option two, "Dragonfly
Cutter 2000-X."
[sigh]
KAZUKI: Option three,
simply "The Lance."
Or four, defying
expectation, "The Sword."
So which will it be?
-That is the last thing
we should worry about!
First, we need to do a search
and identify the enemy!
-And I went to the trouble
of working at it all night.
-So that's the reason
why you're so tired.
Make sure you get some sleep.
-Uh, yes, ma'am.
-I came by earlier and
checked out this area
while you were still at school.
-What's that?
-It's an incubator I
found in the basement
for a homunculus embryo.
-Embryo?
-Created from cells of
living organisms as the base.
They are very fragile
things, 1.2 inches in size
and they can't last
more than a day--
unless they're in an airtight
space like this flask.
However, when that fragile
embryo lodges itself
into a person's brain,
it takes over the flesh,
alters the entire
body, and morphs
into an unyielding
man-eating monster
like the one we saw last night.
-So--
-Mita and Saruwatari were
shadows of their former selves.
An embryo takes over
one body but more will
be sacrificed to feed.
-That means there'll
be more victims.
-Yes, that's right.
Someone who knows the
results of his actions
conducted these experiments
here and created these monsters.
And there's only one thing that
can stop them and nothing else,
and that is our Buso Renkin.
-Can I ask you something?
-Hmm?
-I just can't figure it out.
Who could be doing research
on these monsters here
and for what purpose?
-There is a high school
boy and a high school girl,
but the girl is wearing a
uniform I've never seen before.
The boy wears a uniform from
the same school as you master.
Should we attack?
I'm confident I can take
them out from where we are.
-Not yet.
I think we should be
polite and approach
in a more friendly manner.
[bubbling liquid]
-Obviously, someone
living in this area
is involved with alchemy.
We could speculate about
what their purpose is,
but we can't say for
sure at this stage.
What we can say for sure is
that the creator does not
have any bit of
respect for human life.
He will do whatever it takes
for the sake of his research.
[ping]
[gasp]
-Tokiko!
TOKIKO: Don't touch me.
-It has been deflected.
-Too bad.
I thought we'd be able to do
some Kakugane research if we
got close, but I guess
it won't be possible.
Washio, now go and attack.
[grunt]
-It's up above.
-Buso Renkin!
-He's coming.
Throw your lance into this sky.
With the power of
your Buso Renkin,
it will reach him quicker.
-But how?
-Your Buso Renkin is
a part of yourself
that's coming from
your fighting instinct.
You have the power to do it.
Just believe.
-I got it.
Pierce through, my Buso Renkin!
[gasp]
-Evade the attack.
-I won't let you get away.
-Isn't this a surprise?
An Alchemist Warrior,
how interesting.
[chuckling]
-Valkyrie Skirt!
He's fast.
-Are you all right, Master?
-Yes, I'm fine.
But I shouldn't underestimate
that death scythe girl--
and the other one, the
boy with the lance.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
That school uniform.
This guy is from the
same school as Kazuki.
It's a start.
-Tokiko!
Are you all right?
Tokiko!
[clang]
[shuddering grunts]
-Are you all right, Kazuki?
-Uh huh.
-There were a total of 20
incubators underground.
We defeated 16
homunculi last night.
Add the wretched embryo
I repelled off earlier.
That leaves three homunculi
enemies left and the Papillon
Masked Creator, the one who
wears the Papillon mask.
The remaining three
are most likely
there to safeguard the creator.
It's not going to be easy.
-I agree.
We definitely gotta win.
-That's right.
The Buso Renkin was specifically
created to exterminate them.
We'll beat them no matter what.
We cannot lose.
-We won't just beat them.
We'll have to prevent any
further victims from dying.
That's the only way we
can obtain true victory.
I'm going to go pay my respects
at the gravesite once more.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): He makes
the most difficult task
sound so easy.
However--
TOKIKO: Wait.
-Hmm?
TOKIKO: I'll go with you.
-That was really
something up there.
I wonder what in the
world that big thing was?
DAIHAMA: Hmm.
Maybe a plastic bottle rocket.
MAHIRO: Who knows?
-Hah.
All right, come on.
Who cares?
Let's get going, I won't
let him get away with this.
He has to introduce me.
Puh!
MAHIRO: Can it be true?
My big brother really meeting
a woman in a place like that?
OKAKURA: I'll catch him
strawberrying there.
[heartbeat]
-Kazuki.
-What is it, Tokiko?
-You've obtained
power, you know.
-Mm-hmm.
-But that alone will not
be enough to prevent there
from being more victims.
If your main purpose is to
prevent there being any more
victims, then you must
understand how imperative
it is to fully commander
your Buso Renkin.
MAHIRO: Oh!
There he is!
Yoo-hoo, Kazuki!
-Did you tell them we were
going to be coming here?
-No, I didn't.
-Well, that's fine.
You're going to have
to handle this alone.
I'm leaving.
-Why would you want to
come to a place like this?
-Ooh, I can't believe it!
It's true, you've
got a girlfriend!
-Huh?
-Kazuki!
-Uh, I, I wha--
-Congratulations.
-Please tell us the details.
-So since when?
Tell me, tell me, I wanna know?
-My girlfriend?
What?
Me?
Her?
I, well, um, uh--
-I see.
So I'm your girlfriend, huh?
Very interesting.
-Uh.
[gasps]
-(IN UNISON) We're
so very sorry.
-If you're not his girlfriend,
then who exactly are you?
-(IN UNISON) We're siblings.
[gasp]
-A big sister?
Wait a minute, nobody told me.
-Yeah.
-Oh!
But you have a different last
name, don't you, big sister?
-Oh, this is wonderful.
Can you come up with
something better than this?
-Um, the only thing
I can think of
is you being my teacher
or maybe my rival.
[groan]
-Hmm, Kazuki's girlfriend
is his teacher.
MAHIRO (VOICEOVER): So
if she's his sister,
then she has to be mine too.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): Yeah!
[laughter]
-Oh, this is all so confusing.
-Oh, you're so
freakin' lucky, Kazuki!
DAIHAMA: Kazuki
and the girlfriend
say they are rivals, but--
-Ah!
So that's it, isn't it?
-I think their
imagination's completely
getting out of control.
[clicking tongue]
-It's all for the best.
[quiet screaming]
-Listen guys, why
don't we go somewhere
to have some tea instead
of standing around here?
-(GIGGLING) I second that.
-It appears that we have
quite a bit to talk about,
so what do you say, hmm?
-I can't.
I have to go and--
all right, why not?
Let's just go.
-All right, everybody!
Then let's all get moving!
-OK.
[gasp]
-Tokiko, look.
-Appears we've run
into some trouble.
I should have destroyed it
instead of just deflecting it.
[sigh]
-Hello, Kawazui.
Are you there?
KAWAZUI (ON PHONE): Aiee!
I'm waiting nearby just
as you ordered, master.
Aiee!
I understand.
All I have to do is
launch an attack, right?
PAPILLON (ON PHONE):
However, there
is no need to pursue too far.
KAWAZUI: Then in that case, I'll
use my little ones this time
around.
Hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee.
[frogs croaking]
-I'll get rid of it now.
-I'm going to help you too.
-No, don't.
You need to stay out of this.
We have to take care of this
without anyone noticing.
DAIHAMA: Where do you
think we should go?
MAHIRO: Hmm, let's see.
Maybe we should go to that
place across the train station.
TOKIKO: We'll end up dragging
them into danger if we fail.
Once the embryo
invades the brain,
there will be nothing
we can do about it.
It'll kill their minds
immediately, take their flesh,
and they'll become
man-eating creatures
that will go on a rampage.
Plus, you don't know how
to activate your Buso
Renkin in a stealth manner.
-Buso Renkin!
-You don't have total command
of the Buso Renkin yet.
All you know right now is a
full strength power technique,
a limited skill in
these situations.
-Hmm.
TOKIKO: My Valkyrie Skirt
is quick and accurate--
four arms for four targets.
It can easily pinpoint a
moving target with precision.
Now let's see who
it's going to go for.
-It's moving.
-I'm the target.
-Tokiko, look out!
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): We
have to take care of this
without anyone noticing.
We'll end up dragging them
into danger if we fail.
-Damn it.
-Hm?
-What in the hell?
-Hey, where did they go?
-Looks like they've escaped.
Hmm.
-Kazuki!
-I wonder where they
could have gone.
-You know something?
I'm not sure what kind
of person she really is.
-Hmm.
MAHIRO (VOICEOVER): Her
voice sounds so familiar.
I feel like I've heard
it somewhere before.
[grunting]
-Oh, that's gonna hurt.
Oh no!
[clang]
[gasp]
-So you're finally awake, huh?
The sun went down
a long time ago.
-Are you OK?
-You're the one with
bruises-- all over your body.
-Aah!
Gah!
[yelling]
-I'm going to be fine now.
Thanks to you,
Kazuki, I wasn't hurt.
-What about the
homunculus embryo?
-It's not dead, but I was
able to avert invasion
into the brain because of you.
[gasp]
[grunt]
-Uh--
[sigh]
-I'm sorry.
-Why are you apologizing?
You haven't done anything wrong.
-All the same, I'm sorry.
-Don't apologize.
In fact, you did extremely well.
If your little sister or your
friends had been inhabited,
then there would have
been no turning back.
The same goes for you as well.
You know, putting your life
in danger unnecessarily is not
something I want you
to do over and over.
Anyway, we're going to have
to take care of business
before this wretched parasite
makes its way into my head
and takes over.
-Then there's hope!
-Well, if that
weren't the case, I
would have certainly
finished myself off way
before you would have
even opened your eyes.
At this point, it will probably
take about a week or so
for the embryo to reach
the brain from my body.
Before then, we have to defeat
the three homunculi monsters
standing in the way and
capture the Papillon Masked
Creator, the only one
who can create a cure.
If we don't make it, I will
turn into a homunculus.
And when that happens,
you will have to kill me.
[gasp]
TOKIKO: That's just how it is.
[grunt]
-We don't have
any time to waste.
We must attack first.
Buso-- ugh!
It's trying to interfere.
-Tokiko!
[grunt]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Renkin activation
without any sound or movement?
-Don't you even think
about touching her.
[frogs croaking]
-What?
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): This is bad.
His Buso Renkin lance ill-suited
for minute movement as it is.
Also, all he still
knows is how to use
his main powerful technique.
However, his current skills--
[frogs croaking]
[grunt]
[yell]
-Pierce through, my Buso Renkin!
Yaa!
Hyaa!
[panting]
[grunt]
-Are you still in pain, Tokiko?
Just endure a bit more.
One more week.
-Hm.
-I'm going to master this lance
in a week, no matter what,
and capture the Papillon
Masked Creator, I promise.
[music playing]
[MUSIC - YOSHIAKI DEWA,
"HOSHIAKARI"]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
At this rate,
I'll become a
homunculus in a week.
When that happens,
you'll have to kill me.
Next time-- "You've
Become a Little Stronger."
I'll splatter your guts!
[music playing]
MAHIRO (VOICEOVER):
Mahiro's Buso Renkin Corner!
Mahiro's Buso Renkin
seminar starts now.
Yay!
Da de da da!
Da de de da da da da de da.
From today on, I,
Mahiro Muto, will
be introducing the many eclectic
and exciting Buso Renkin
to the viewers.
And to kick off
our first seminar,
let me present Kazuki Muto's
Buso Renkin, the Sunlight
Heart.
As you know, Kazuki
Muto is a super klutz
who possesses a very
strong sense of justice.
I'm proud of my big brother
because he cares so much
for his friends and others.
But his kindhearted nature also
caused him to get in trouble.
That's what got him
killed by the homunculus
in the first place.
Kazuki was fortunate enough
to come back to life,
thanks to Tokiko, who implanted
a Kakugane as a replacement
for his heart.
And using that Kakugane,
he made the vow
to fight and protect everyone.
So anyway, Kazuki's Buso
Renkin looks like a sword,
but it's really a lance.
How fitting for my
reckless big brother.
Using his lance, he charges
into the enemy with a bang!
But the ornament cloth
attached to the lance
is really what makes
this Buso Renkin special.
The cloth responds
to the bearer's will
to fight and energizes
itself, emanating
a beautiful orange color.
Inspired by this luminous
color, Tokiko gave the lance
the name of Sunlight Heart.
Kazuki also came up
with several names,
but I think Sunlight
Heart is a much nicer one.
Don't tell him I said that.
Anyway, even though my
big brother has much
learn from Tokiko, I
know we can count on him.
And that's why he's there
for everyone, no matter who
they are.
Okie dokie, tune in
for our next seminar.
[giggling]