NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
-Clean out your
ears and listen up.
I'm about to tell you everything
there is to know about the LXE.
But before that, Tokiko,
get down on your knees.
-Huh?
-You need to apologize, because
when you two were fighting,
you tried to kill Ouka.
And if she dies, I'll disappear
along with her, you witch!
If you had killed
Ouka and Shusui,
you wouldn't be getting
any info, now, would you?
Show some respect, you moron!
You're not so bright, are you?
You're a failure as a warrior!
It's clear, already!
-Calm down.
-Despite her appearance,
Warrior Tokiko is very gifted.
Even though she can
get out of control
when she loses her temper.
-Trust me, deep down
she's very nice.
But she'll want to
splatter your guts.
-You both better apologize.
-Ow!
-It'll get dark very soon,
so let's get to this.
The League of
Extraordinary Elects,
commonly known as the LXE--
-Basically, the skinny is--
BRAVO: The LXE is a community
of Homunculi and Familiars
in the northern Kanto area.
The number of Homunculi,
the number of Familiars,
and the number of
Kakugane are all unknown.
-That's no good.
-Just pathetic.
-Come on, give me a break!
It's not even my fault!
Ouka's just a maneater now!
-But now we know
where their hideout
is, a cottage in the forest on
the outskirts of Ginsei City.
Ideally I'd want to bring
them down with bigger numbers
to just get rid of them,
but we can't wait for that.
It is possible that
the Traitor Warrior
could recover at any moment.
-And before that happens, we
must defeat Dr. Butterfly!
-The mission will
begin in 13 hours,
tomorrow morning at 8:00.
-I'll be ready.
-Uh, Captain Bravo?
Is that Kazuki gonna be OK?
He's looking a little
stiff and nervous to me.
-I don't blame him.
It's his first major battle.
-Yes, but you know the
enemy won't take that
into consideration.
-But I believe that he is
worthy of being a Warrior.
Of that, I have no doubt.
-All right, then.
Let's take a look at
current global issues.
-Aw, come on.
Isn't there anything more
interesting written in there?
Hey, you're finally here.
-You're really late.
What were you doing?
-Yeah, he's right.
What happened, Kazuki?
-What are you guys doing?
-What's it look like?
Waiting for you is
what we're doing.
-The hospital visit
went well, right?
How is Ouka doing?
-She's fine.
Hey guys, how did
you know it was me?
It's pretty dark.
How could you see my face?
-Come on.
We've been hanging out
together since junior year.
-You know better than that.
-We don't have to see your
silly face in order for us
to tell it's you.
-I guess not.
BOY: So, Ouka is going to be
hospitalized a while longer,
huh?
BOY: I wonder what Shisui
is gonna do about school?
-You know, this
is like old times,
when we used to hang out between
meals at the convenience store.
-Yeah, right after school,
back in junior high.
I remember.
-That's true.
But we haven't done it as much
since we started high school.
Especially lately.
-That's because
a certain someone
has been completely
obsessed with Tokiko lately.
-I don't recall being
obsessed, but OK, OK.
I'm really sorry.
-Wow, spring break passed
by without us really
doing anything together.
-Well, why don't we
make some definite plans
for summer vacation?
-The beach!
Let's go to the beach!
-Sounds good!
-All right, the beach it is!
-And don't forget, Kazuki.
Make sure you bring
Tokiko along with us.
You got that?
-OK.
-It doesn't look like
we'll be able to avoid
a decisive battle.
I'm going to have
you fight as well.
-I'd be delighted to.
By the way, what about adding
Papillon to our forces?
I think he could be quite
useful, in his own way.
-No.
He's no good.
-Oh, is that so?
-He's a failure who
couldn't follow through,
despite the fact he
used my research.
He became an
incomplete Homunculus.
He can't go on his
own-- because if he did,
the Alchemist Warriors would
find him and just destroy him.
We both may be butterflies,
but he's a good for nothing
who can't fly high
or go far by himself.
However, he is still, more
or less, a Homunculus,
so I am protecting him
as a matter of principle,
and nothing else.
-So, I can't fly high
or go far by myself,
huh, Great Grandfather?
Well, we're just going to
have to see about that.
Buso Renkin!
[scream] It's been a long time.
This feeling, the
excruciating pain.
And this agony.
I'd almost forgotten the ecstacy
of near death for a while.
Thanks for protecting me until
now, dear Great Grandfather.
As a sign of gratitude,
now I'll show you
just how well I can really fly!
-Hey, morning, Mahiro.
Have you seen Kazuki?
-Hey, guys.
Actually, I haven't
seen him this morning.
-Really?
Well anyway, listen, we were
thinking of going to the beach
this summer.
-I wanna go!
Can I, can I?
-Of course.
-All right!
Yay!
-Well, I checked out some
possible places on the internet
last night.
Hey Mahiro, where's
Kazuki this morning?
-By the way, Tokiko, do
you know how to swim?
-What are you talking about?
Are you making fun of me?
-Well, the guys were talking
about going to the beach
this summer.
-Do we have to
talk about it now?
-Warrior Kazuki, you can
leave the driving to me.
Oh, yeah!
-Roger that.
-Warrior Chief--
-But before that, we're
going to eliminate
the scourge of alchemy that's
grown thick in this lab.
-Hm?
BRAVO: Deep inside this cottage
is Dr. Butterfly's laboratory.
-All right.
We're ready!
-Wait a minute!
-What is it, Angel Gozen?
-It's going to explode if
you don't unlock it properly
by answering with
the correct password.
MOONFACE: Give me the password.
-Don't worry, I'll tell
you guys the password.
And with the last
part of the password,
it is very important that you
strike a cool, killer pose.
-Strike a pose?
You kidding?
No way I'll ever do a
silly thing like that.
-Let's do it, Tokiko!
-Let's do it, Warrior Tokiko!
-Why are you two so into this?
-What are you going to do?
If we don't all do it,
it's not going to open.
-Will you shut up?
MOONFACE: In one hand--
-A pistol.
-Wait!
Don't start yet!
MOONFACE: In one's heart--
-A boquet of flowers.
Tokiko, please.
MOONFACE: On one's lips--
-Liquor of fire.
MOONFACE: On one's back--
-Now!
Life!
-Life!
-I guess opening the door
with the enemy outside
would have been pretty stupid.
-Hm.
Very true, Bravo.
-They'd better not think
they can get away that easily
after making a fool out of me.
Buso Renkin!
Let's go!
Warrior Chief!
-Yes.
I'd heard they ley down
their guard during the day,
but it is strange that we
haven't encountered anyone
as well.
-Over here, Kazuki!
Come on!
-Let's go!
Sunlight Slasher!
-So, this is the lowest
level of the LXE hideout.
-That means this is Dr.
Butterfly's laboratory.
[shouting]
-What's the matter, Angel Gozen?
-It's gone!
-Hat are you talking about?
-The heart of the laboratory!
The tank!
It's gone!
-That is because his body
is almost fully restored.
Now all he needs to do is
feed, and he will resurrect.
Which is why Dr. Butterfly
has taken the body with him.
-Are you a humanoid Homunculus?
-Course I am.
My name used to be
Lunare Nikolaev.
Now I'm Moonface, and this
is my precious Buso Renkin.
-Where's Dr. Butterfly?
Where did he go?
-That's a pretty easy
quiz, don't you think?
There is a nearby place
filled with young life,
and that place is--
-Oh, no.
Don't tell me.
-Ginsei Academy?
-That's correct.
-Direct Hit, Bravo Punch!
-Let's hurry.
Everyone's in danger.
-Moon.
If you ask me, I
think it's a joke
to send inexperienced kids
to a battle like this.
-Trust me, you don't
have to worry about them.
I just need to take down
the one enemy left here,
and then go join 'em.
And that'll be taken care
of with one swift attack.
-Moon!
I suppose.
However, that's if there's
only one of me left.
-Huh?
-Oh, please let us
make it in time.
I hope everyone's safe!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What's that up ahead?
-Hey!
That's coming from the school.
BOY: Where's it coming from?
-Did you guys see?
There's a ton of fog outside.
-I can't see outside
the school at all.
-All right, everyone.
Get back to class right away.
-What's wrong with
my cell phone?
It's not working.
-Neither is mine.
-Quiet down.
The teachers are trying to find
out what's going on outside.
So in the meantime,
let's just remain calm.
Mr. Takagishi,
what's the matter?
-There's no way out.
-Huh?
-I was heading to the school
gate, but before I knew it,
I ended up back where I started.
It's like being lost in a maze.
This fog isn't natural.
-Hey guys, is my
brother here yet?
-No.
Neither he nor
Tokiko have come yet.
-Something isn't right.
I think it'd be better
if you stay here with us.
-OK.
But I'm just gonna go get
Chii-chin and Sally first.
-Hey!
What's that?
There's something strange
in the schoolyard.
[frightened conversations]
MAN: My GPS isn't working!
-What's going on with
the traffic light?
-I had the right
of way, you idiot!
-Whoa!
Look out!
[whistle]
-Chief!
-Hey!
So how did it go?
-Actually, no.
No matter what I do, I
can't seem to get past here.
-I don't understand.
What's up ahead, anyway?
-If I remember correctly, it's
the Ginesei Private Academy.
-Tokiko, this fog it's--
-You noticed the
strangeness of it, too.
Stay sharp.
If you look really
carefully, there
are metal particles
mixed in with it.
This is a Buso Renkin.
The special property throws off
peoples' sense of direction,
and isolates what's inside of
the fog from what's outside.
-Dammit.
Which way?
ANGEL GOZEN: This way, Kazuki!
-Angel Gozen?
You know the way?
-My angel eyes are clear,
and can see far and wide.
Come on, let's go.
Quick, follow me!
-OK!
-Listen to me, Kazuki.
Make sure you cover your face.
It wouldn't be a good thing
if the students at the school
were able to recognize you.
-Sure.
But what about you, Tokiko?
-With my long hair and
this fog, I should be OK.
But the problem is this uniform.
-Got it.
-OK, here they are.
-Good.
Uh, Mappy, are you sure that
we can leave class like this?
-Don't worry about it.
The teachers haven't
been able to do
anything about this
situation anyway.
-And no matter what happens,
we're here to protect you.
So no worries.
-To be honest, I am scared.
But we should at least be able
to buy some time to escape.
-Hey, those things in the
schoolyard started moving!
GIRL: Oh, no!
They're coming this way!
-What the hell are those things?
[roar]
-Feed us!
[screaming]
-We've gotta get out of here!
-Run!
-Run, everybody!
-The revised humanoid Homunculi.
I set out to create
Homunculi that
can fight Alchemist Warriors.
Even without Buso Renkin.
As I thought, they are
still far inferior to you.
Nevertheless, I do take
pride in having completed
a very good specimen, with
pretty decent combat abilities.
-Feed me!
[screaming]
-Buso Renkin!
-We made it just in time.
-So, the Alchemist Warriors
have finally appeared.
-Here we come, you monsters!
-There's no way I'll let you
get any closer to the school
building!
[shout]
-What?
-Are they fighting the monsters?
-Who are those two?
[shout]
BOY: Wait!
Are they all
fighting each other?
BOY: No.
Just two of them look human.
-Huh?
-But to think they can
fight those monsters.
-Are those two human?
-No!
Actually, those two are--
INTERCOM: Monsters.
-Huh?
-Monsters are
attacking the academy.
Let's all work together
and protect the school.
This is Student Council
Secretary and Proxy President
Suzuki Shinyo speaking to you.
The school currently has no
contact with the outside world.
We've been completely cut off.
Until help arrives, we must
not let the monsters fighting
outside approach
the school building.
-Are all of them
really monsters?
-Shut up, you idiot.
-All right.
Okakura, Daihama.
-I'm ready.
-Let's go!
INTERCOM: They're all monsters.
Whether or not they have
taken on human form,
all of them in the
schoolyard are monsters.
Do not let them
in, no matter what!
-No!
-Chii-chin?
-They're monsters, just
like that last time!
They look human, but
they're monsters!
All of them!
-Oh, Chii-chin!
-Just hang in there!
BOY: What's going on down there?
Look at the size of them!
It's huge!
INTERCOM: Everyone's help
is absolutely necessary
to protect the school
from the monsters.
Let's show them our strength.
We'll all protect
the school together.
-BOY: Stay away!
Get out, monster!
-Stay back!
-Yeah!
-Get outta here!
BOY: We'll fight
together to get you out!
-What are you doing?
They're risking their lives
to protect all you guys!
KAZUKI: It's OK, Angel Gozen.
-Huh?
-This isn't the time to
convince them who we are.
-He's absolutely right.
This is the time to fight.
-Oh, Kazuki.
-Show your defiance and
your will to resist.
Bags, notebooks, desks, chairs.
They may not be
much individually,
but they will
certainly chip away
at the monsters' will to fight.
Let's all work
together, and fight out
those horrible monsters!
Heh, heh, heh.
-Ha.
Attacking with backdoor tactics.
Clever idea, Familiar Suzuki.
This attack should
make a deep impression
on this greenhorn still
wet behind the ears.
-Kazuki!
-Dammit!
SUZUKI: One of them is injured.
Get him!
-I've-- I've gotta
get it together.
-Kazuki!
SUZUKI: Everyone, we need
to beat those monsters
down at once!
-Dammit, it won't open.
-It must be locked
from the inside.
-Daihama, why don't
you give it a try?
-I don't know.
Let's see.
-Daihama?
-Moron!
Quit talking nonsense!
-What do you mean, nonsense?
I'm doing this
broadcast to protect
the school from the monsters.
I'm just serving the students.
That's all.
-You're an idiot.
-Huh?
-Listen, Suzuki.
The problem is you're
assuming that everything
in the schoolyard is
a monster or an enemy,
and you're broadcasting
that as true.
But aren't the two who
came later and began
fighting the monsters humans,
just like the rest of us?
-Rokumasu?
SUZUKI: There is
absolutely no way
in the world ordinary
humans could fight
at even terms against such
a huge army of monsters.
-Try using your common sense.
-Can't you see that
common sense doesn't
apply in a situation like this?
-Huh?
-Does this situation seem
normal to you, Suzuki?
-It doesn't really
matter, since none of us
know who those individuals are.
I still think it's
very dangerous
to assume that they are
on our side, don't you?
-Well, we happen to
know who they are.
-Those two people out there--
- --are our very good friends.
SUZUKI: Talk about being
driven by distress.
Friends?
On what basis?
We can't even see their
faces in this fog.
And not to mention
that one of them
is clearly trying to
conceal his identity.
-We know who he is.
-Even if we can't
see his moronic face.
-We can recognize him.
ROKUMASU: The ones fighting
out there are our friends.
They are friends--
TOGETHER: To us all!
-That's right, you fool!
-Huh?
-That fool out there
is such an idiot!
He's gone so far as to save
the life of an enemy who
even tried to kill him!
He's not stupid!
A super, duper, ultra,
mega huge idiot.
But idiot or not,
there's no way a nice guy
like him would try to
hurt you, you morons.
Can't you see that?
-Angel Gozen?
What are you doing here?
-Huh?
ROKUMASU: We heard that, Suzuki.
So tell us.
How do you know
this intruder here?
SUZUKI: Uh, well--
What's going on?
What's happening?
- --our friends or our foes?
-So are the two in the
schoolyard on our side or not?
-Could those two be--
-Get out of the way!
-Get up, Chii-chin!
We have to get out of here!
-I can't.
I'm so scared I
can't move from here.
Run, Sally.
Just run away.
-Chii-chin!
Oh, no!
[shouts]
-It's all right.
I just remembered.
I mentioned it to
you guys before.
A nightmare.
A nightmare a lot like this
that I had around the time
when I first started school.
I see now that it
wasn't a dream.
It really happened.
And in the end, my brother
appeared and saved me.
-I'm gonna eat you.
-I have no doubt he'll come
and protect us this time too,
because this time, he'll
be here for all of us.
I'm sure.
He'll protect everyone!
[theme music]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): The
humanoid Homunculi increase,
Dr. Butterfly's plot
engulfs the school,
and with the sound
of the flask's alarm,
the king of the
Homunculi awakens.
Next episode, Signs of Death!
I'll splatter your guts.