NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name?
Buso Renkin.
[music playing]
-I'm glad you accepted
our challenge.
As you can tell, we
don't need any assistance
or any interference.
So it'll just be
two against two.
The both of you are very
popular with the other students.
If you take advantage of that
popularity to set up a trap,
you could potentially make
victims out dozens of students.
But now that I know
you're enemies,
I'll take you out quick.
Of course we'll accept.
-Oh my.
But do you think you could
wait another 30 minutes
until the security guards
make their final rounds?
After that we can turn
off the security system
and we won't have to worry
about any more interruptions.
And then we'll fight
without reservation.
-You don't look so good, Kazuki.
Do you think you
can fight like that?
When you said you wanted
to become as strong as you
possibly could, I
thought those were
words coming from
a warrior preparing
himself to defeat the enemy.
Were those words just a lie?
-It wasn't a lie.
I meant it.
But I thought you two were
friends, dependable seniors
that we could rely on.
I thought you were people I
was supposed to protect and not
enemies that I'd have to fight.
-That's right.
You did indeed protect
us before, Kazuki.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to
disappoint you, but--
-We don't need
you to protect us.
We can take care of ourselves.
All we need is the power
to make our wish come true.
[footsteps]
-Looks like the second
gymnasium's all clear.
-Yeah, it's all clear.
-Well, that's it for the rounds.
Let's get out of here.
-Yep.
-Alrighty.
Time for a little nap,
Mr. security system.
Now even if windows break or a
fire occurs or if people die,
for that matter, this
school will be all clear
for a couple of hours.
At least until midnight.
-Are they gone?
-Mm-hmm.
Boy, this school
has lousy security.
-Well, that's the
kind of work you
get from unmotivated people.
The same goes for you.
-What?
-A warrior who's not willing to
fight isn't much good either.
So if you don't want to fight
those siblings, then go home.
-Of course I'll fight.
I decided to become a
warrior and I'm here,
ready to protect people
from the Humunculi.
-That's just what I'd
expect you to say.
We would hate to miss
the chance to take out
two warriors at once.
The number of people
now is two against two.
It's time.
Now let's duel.
-But it looks like
Ouka isn't here yet.
-You don't have to concern
yourself with my older sister.
I can take you one at a
time or both together.
And to make up for the
surprise attack earlier,
I'll let you guys
have the first move.
-You pretend to hold up
the spirit of Bushido
despite being a Humunculus?
-Tokiko, I want you
to leave this to me.
Listen, Shusui.
We'll fight one on one like
we've done in sparring.
-Fine, but only until
Ouka Hayasaka shows up.
-Thank you.
Here I go.
Buso Renkin!
He blocked it with a kakugane!
-I granted you the first move.
Now it's my turn.
Let's go.
Buso Renkin!
-Its sharpness, it's not normal.
As I suspected, Shusui
Hayasaka's Buso Renkin
is a katana sword.
-Get ready.
-Unlike the bamboo
sword from practice,
the slightest touch of
that thing could be fatal.
Just focus on that blade.
-Kazuki!
-I'm all right.
I can still handle it.
-Are you sure about that?
I didn't think you'd all so
easily just from this item.
-My plan worked perfectly.
Now we can fight without
wrecking the school.
-Oh, really?
-Good idea.
Very well.
It will also be easier to
clean up your blood out here.
-Here I go!
-One down.
One left.
-So your sister likes
ambush tactics, huh?
That's more like it.
Now you're both
acting like Humunculi.
The roof, huh?
Kazuki, I'll go take
care of the sister
and leave you to
take care of him.
-Your Death Scythes are more
efficient than I thought.
But they will never reach her.
Now, Kazuki, shall you
and I get back to it?
Because of you, I've
had some good training.
Thank you.
You're definitely
getting stronger.
But of course, I am too.
It appears that you and
I get along very well.
-Kazuki.
-Don't worry.
I know.
I just have to think about all
the suffering his sister would
be inflicting upon others.
It's OK.
I can still fight.
Energy full blast!
Sunlight crasher!
-I see.
This special feature of that
lance is that cloth alone.
It materializes
life force energy,
converting it into an attack.
However.
-What?
The energy is fading!
-Any amount of energy
is absorbed by the blade
and then expelled from the
cord that hangs from the hilt.
This is the special
property of my Buso Renkin.
Sword Samurai X.
Your energy based
attacks are useless against me.
-Sunlight crasher!
Again?
-Your attack is in vain.
If the blade directly touches
even part of your weapon,
not only will the
energy be absorbed,
but the impact itself
that is generated even
from that simple brush with your
Buso Renkin is also absorbed.
Any and all energy
attacks become
powerless against the
Sword Samurai X. It really
seems as though you and
I are truly a good match.
-So in other words,
a head to head
battle with just our
raw strength and skills.
Is that it?
-Exactly.
A peer battle between
a sword and a spear.
-Let's go!
-Get down.
That spot is reserved for me.
-Is that so?
Well not tonight.
It's the perfect
place from which
I can shoot my arrows at you
and finally finish you off.
-What?
Did you say that Kazuki and
Tokiko haven't returned yet?
-Yeah, we were with them
up until school let out.
-What is Bravo doing
here at this hour?
-Oh, no need to worry, Bravo.
They do this all the time.
Oh!
Hey, an earthquake.
Look, we're shaking.
It's an earthquake.
-Really?
I don't feel it at all.
-Why are you so excited
about that, Mahiro?
-Earthquake bulletin.
Watch.
-I was fighting the
final boss just now!
Just turn it back on,
please, turn it back on!
[panting]
-You should think a little
more before you attack.
All you're doing is
making holes in the roof.
-Oh, my.
But please tell me,
who's going to report me?
Certainly not you,
since you'll be dead.
-Buso Renkin archery.
The special property
is precise, high speed
shooting with that
stupid looking automaton.
However, that doesn't
explain the gauntlet
she's wearing on her right arm.
She must have another
ability up their sleeve.
-The death scythe Buso Renkin.
Its special property is
precise high speed operation
with a manipulator.
That somewhat resembles
my Buso Renkin.
Isn't that interesting?
However.
But it seems my Angel Gozen
here is slightly more superior,
don't you agree?
-[laughs]
-Huh?
-You know what?
I've had it with you.
I don't want to worry anymore
about taking you alive
or cleaning up afterwards.
So I'm just going to
splatter your guts.
-What?
Master Gozen, fire now.
She's sacrificing her arms and
legs to protect her vitals.
It's impossible to
shoot her down this way.
Master Gozen, go now.
-I missed.
No.
Something made me miss.
Oh, come on you
stupid little doll.
Get off me.
Beat it.
Her Buso has been deactivated.
She's on the run.
-I ambush and then I
escape and the end result
is me looking like this.
How pathetic.
But I don't care how much
I need to endure in order
to make our dream come true.
She's not an opponent
I can handle by myself.
I can't take her down alone.
I must meet up with
Shusui and regroup.
I wonder how things
are going for him.
-14 cuts.
You lasted longer
than I thought.
Kazuki, I'm grateful to you.
The only reason I am
as strong as I am now
is because of all the
training that I've
done with you this week.
Thanks to you I am as
strong as I possibly can be.
And now thanks to
your death, I've
arrived closer to
my greatest desire.
It must be lonely
to die on your own.
Be sure to wait a bit at the
entrance of the afterlife.
I'll send along one more person.
Tokiko Tsumura
will join you soon.
-I'm not dead yet.
And I won't let Tokiko
die either, you hear me?
-How can you still be alive?
You've got fatal
wounds in 14 spots.
-You're the only one, Shusui.
I too got as strong
as I possibly
could after this one
week of training.
I suppose that's one thing
I'll have to thank you for.
-He was able to dodge that.
But my physical
ability and skills
are still greater than his.
He is definitely much
stronger than before though.
Now that I think about it.
Tell me something, Kazuki.
Have you had some
other training?
-I've been receiving
basic training
as an alchemist
warrior every night.
-So you've been training
twice as much as I have, huh?
No wonder you've improved
as much as you have.
-I'm the most inexperienced
warrior of my entire group,
so I have to work the hardest.
And that's what I'll do.
What's that wish you
talked about earlier?
You're wanting to get as
strong as you possibly could,
for the sake of making
that wish come true?
What the hell is
the wish that you
want so badly that you'd
give up being human?
-It's not my wish alone.
It is also my sister's.
If you really want to
know, I'll tell you.
However--
-His fighting spirit.
It must be from--
-Only if you can stop my
sword with your lance.
-The Reverse Do!
It's beyond my power to
dodge that kind of speed.
And it's also possible to
block that kind of weight.
It's Shusui's ultimate attack.
Once he unleashes it--
-You will die.
I'm going to kill you.
The attack will
be instantaneous.
Close your eyes and
relax your arms and legs.
If you do that, you won't
have to feel any pain or fear.
-When you let me have
the first move earlier,
you were acting according
to your own principles
in order to ease
your own conscience.
But if you're willing
to give up your humanity
for this desire of yours,
I should know what it is.
I have the right to
know that much at least.
-You should know that can't
dodge nor block my Reverse Do.
The other option
is to take the hit
and attempt to counter attack.
Then you might be
able to take me out.
But my Sword Samurai X can slice
through both flesh and bone
at once, First I'll
take your life,
and then I'll take your
kakugane at my leisure.
-Unfortunately, my life and
kakugane are one in the same.
Not even you will be
able to cut through that.
And I'll prove it.
-Kazuki.
I've cut through his vitals.
But what's this?
-I deactivated my Buso Renkin.
You blocked my first
move with your kakugane.
So now it's my turn to
do the same thing to you.
This kakugane that I received
from Tokiko is a new life.
And there's no way I'm going
to give it up just like that.
Once again.
Buso!
-No!
-Ouka.
What are you?
-Shusui.
-What the?
The wound is
transferring to Ouka.
-Ouka.
Stop it.
No.
-Her Buso Renkin
transfers injuries.
-Ouka.
-Shusui.
-But a wound like that
should automatically
heal in a Humunculus.
Wounds in areas other
than the emblem mark
should not be fatal.
And yet, why?
Could it be that these two
are flesh and blood humans?
-Familiars.
-Tokiko?
-Your wounds.
Are you OK?
-They're hurting.
But I'll deal with it.
What did you say they were?
-I guess I didn't
tell you, did I?
Familiars are human
beings who pledge loyalty
to the Humunculi.
No matter how superior
they are to humans,
a Humunculus as
a single body has
difficulty to survive
alone hidden in society.
Each time they eat a
human it becomes easier
to be spotted by an
alchemist warrior.
And if they're
discovered, they're
almost always terminated.
Consequently, communities like
the L.X.E. Are usually formed.
And humans like these
two are incorporated
at the bottom of that
social hierarchy.
Those who have authority
and financial status
supply that power and those with
nothing become manual labor.
-The emblem.
-Look closely.
It's just fluorescent paint.
Familiars paint an
emblem on themselves
as a form of prevention when
they work for the Humunculi.
This is supposedly
done to prevent them
from being devoured by mistake.
So this confirms everything.
-Shusui, Ouka, why do this?
-I promised that
I would tell you
if you stopped my Reverse Do.
We both share the same desire.
We want to become Humunculi
so that we can live together
for all eternity.
We both made our pledge
in sickness and health.
-We pledged in joy
and also in sorrow.
-For richer.
-Or for poorer.
-To love and respect.
-To comfort and protect.
-Til death do us part.
[music playing]
-That softness of yours will
cost you your life someday.
Before that happens I will take
away your fighting strength
and I'll put an end to
your life as a warrior.
Next episode, Til
Death Do Us Part.
I'll splatter your guts.