NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name?
Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
-Brobdingnab Finger Strike!
-But I do have a weapon.
My thoroughly trained
warrior body is my weapon.
-Ha!
-I told you already,
I'm not angry.
At all!
-OK, I'll do it.
If we allow the LXE
to continue to exist,
this town will go to pieces.
Captain Bravo, please make
me into an alchemist warrior.
-Kazuki Muto, you can't always
rely on your Buso Renkin alone.
If you keep on fighting the way
you have been all this time,
you'll never win, and
you'll get yourself killed.
In order to make you into
an Alchemist Warrior,
I'll train you without mercy.
If you don't want to
parish, sink your teeth
in with a do or die resolve.
Got it?
-Hm.
-Same goes for you,
warrior Tokiko.
Protecting rookies is my duty.
So leave Muto to me from now on.
Go and recover your
warrior instincts.
If you don't,
you'll be defeated--
and get yourself killed.
BOY: Hey.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Did you see that on the roof?
I know I saw something.
BOY: Did you guys see that?
-Whoa.
Looks like we've drawn a crowd.
-We should avoid them.
Let's go.
-Hyahoo!
-He's alive!
-I avoided striking his vitals.
We need to get him to tell
us information about the LXE.
-You gotta be joking.
If I were to do
something like that,
who knows what Dr. Butterfly
would end up doing to me?
-Don't worry about it.
You'll end up wanting
to talk regardless
of what's in store for you.
-I'm not so sure about that.
-Good work, Kinjo.
I will let you die quickly.
-Thank you, Jinnai.
-He killed his own comrade.
-In order to silence him.
-You may keep the
Kakugane for the moment,
but I'll be back to
retrieve it soon.
Homunculi can be
easily replaced.
But unfortunately,
Kakugane cannot.
So it is my duty to recover it.
Until next time.
-This is not my day.
Why are we the ones
who have to carry this?
-I know, I know.
Just don't drop it.
-Who the hell is he?
-From the drama club?
-Wrong answer.
Now, for your own sake,
better not get involved.
[screaming]
-Kakugane.
So I guess even this
small fry gets one.
But I don't, huh?
This is most unpleasant.
-There are three
things we are sure of.
First of all is
that Papillon still
doesn't have a Kakugane
like the rest of us do.
It seems his man-eating appetite
has regressed for the time
being, so therefore we can put
off dealing with him for now.
Secondly, there's the LXE.
All their actions so
far seem to indicate
that they don't
have the slightest
intention of launching any sort
of all out attack against us.
This is probably because
their strongest LXE member,
the Warrior Traitor, has
not fully recovered yet.
Of course, there's
no reason for us
to wait until they're
ready to strike.
We must locate their hideout,
make a quick assessment
of their numbers, and wipe
them out in a single blow.
Third and finally,
there's you, Muto.
Just as Warrior
Tokiko has reported,
your sunlight heart is
indeed very powerful.
However, for now
it's pretty clear
that you are not able to
beat a humanoid Homunculus
on your own.
-I need training.
-Special training.
We'll start today.
-I'm ready.
-Warrior Chief,
I'd like to assist
in Kazuki's special training.
-Afraid not.
I've got a different
mission in mind for you.
-Seconds, please.
Thank you for a delicious meal.
-I won.
-Not bad.
It's a draw.
All right.
Time to go.
Ready, Muto?
-Yeah, Bravo.
You bet I am.
As a matter of fact, I'm a
master of special training.
-Bravo.
I'm also a master
of special training.
-Special training?
What do you mean?
-Well, it's a secret.
Because--
-It's just cooler that way.
-Ah!
Kazuki and Captain Bravo left.
You're not gonna go with them?
-Not today.
-Oh, really?
Well, that's a first.
-Well, it happens sometimes.
-Oh, I what.
You can hang out with
me and the girls.
-No, that's all right.
That's not really
my thing, thanks.
-Then how about if a guy
was to hang out, too?
-That's not what I meant.
-I'm in!
So what are we gonna play, huh?
-Othello!
-But only two people
can play that.
-What do you think, Chii-chin?
-I like to play Memory.
I guess.
-See that?
Chii-chin just loves
to play Memory.
-Do you have any idea, Tokiko?
-No, really.
Thanks, but I'll pass.
-Oh, but why?
Come on.
-I'm so sorry.
Some other time, OK?
-Guess not today.
Maybe another time.
Sounds like a deal to me.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Why'd I say I'm sorry?
I didn't have to
apologize for anything.
-Ha.
So there it is.
BRAVO: I've got a different
mission in mind for you.
In a battle between
an Alchemist Warrior
and a humanoid
Homunculus, Kakugane
is exactly like I Shogi piece.
If you have it, it is
a huge asset in battle.
But if you lose it, the enemy
will use it against you.
I want you to safeguard this.
They'll try to get back.
I'll be focusing on
Kazuki's special training.
-But sir, I can help
with the special training
and hang on to the
Kakugane at the same time.
-Like I said, just leave
the protection of the rookie
to me, all right?
You're too protective
of Kazuki Muto.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): He's right.
During the whole
Papillon thing, I
was more worried about
protecting Kazuki than anything
else, even with a Homunculus
right in front of me.
BRAVO (VOICEOVER): Go and
recover your warrior instincts.
If you don't, you
will be defeated,
and get yourself killed.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
My warrior instincts.
Huh.
What's this?
-Buso Renkin.
Noisy Hamelin.
TOKIKO (VOCIEOVER):
Ultrasonic waves?
Oscillating waves.
Whatever it is, it's
piercing my ears.
It's the enemy's attack.
-All right, then.
Begin looking for the
important treasure
in there, my pretty little pets.
[white noise]
-Hm?
Hm?
[music playing]
-Am I imagining things?
-Dammit.
A tracking device.
-I've been detected.
Too late.
I'm already here.
Now that I've made
it this far, I
can follow everything by
sound, and my adorable pets
will do the rest for me.
[groaning]
JINNAI: What will you do now?
Anyone who has their
brains affected
by the sound of my Noisy Hamelon
become my ally, and your enemy.
-Kakugane.
[groaning]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Hypnotic control.
The effects of the
sound waves from before.
Then that means--
the enemy is not far.
He must be within ear
range, and in the direction
the wave originated from.
BOY: Tokiko!
-Kazuki?
-What's up?
I'm Kazuki.
-Sorry.
Just hold still
for a bit, Tokiko.
OK?
-Yes, I am a pervert.
A really good one, at that!
Ha ha!
-Let go of me.
-Huh?
-I'm warning you,
don't touch me.
-I'll touch you!
Tokiko's so soft and
smooth-skinned, yes.
Toki, where's the Kakugane?
Give me the Kakugane!
Give it to me!
[groaning]
-Kakugane.
-Bravo Backbreaker!
Bravo Octopus Hold.
Bravo Rotation Throw!
Ah, ha ha!
All right!
That's it for the warm up.
-Tell me, does a rotation
count as a warm up?
-Bravo.
We'll start the special training
after a 10 minute break.
-Oh.
Can I ask you something?
-Huh?
-We still don't know how
organized the LXE is, right?
What if they are the kind
of opponents the three of us
might not be able
to handle alone?
-If that's the case,
what would you do?
-Call the police?
-I see.
Well-- and tell me, how
would you explain it to them?
-Hm.
-Kakugane.
[groaning]
-I'm surrounded.
[laughter]
-That's correct.
Your opposition are
actually humans,
so there's nothing you can do.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
What should I do?
-Where's the Kakugane?
Give me the Kakugane.
Give me--
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Just
you wait, Homunculus.
-I guess that was kind of a
stupid question, wasn't it?
-It's absolutely natural
to think that way.
But remember,
you've now set foot
in an extraordinary world
of supernatural proportions.
-Extraordinary world.
-The only ones who can
stop an uncommon enemy
like the Homunculi are those of
us who share a similar reality.
No one else could
handle such an opponent.
No matter how strong
the enemy may be,
or how difficult the
battle sometimes may seem,
we must defeat them.
Because we are
Alchemist Warriors.
-Hm!
JINNAI: The Alchemist
Warrior-- he is approaching.
But how?
How did she-- how was she
able to get past my pets?
Could it be she slashed
through all of them?
She used her Buso Renkin
to run on the walls!
-I've found you,
Homunculus beast.
-I guess I'll retreat
for the time being.
-I won't let you get away.
Chii-chin!
-I'll just go to the bathroom,
and then head to bed.
-Look out!
-She looks tasty.
I'll devour her, so
that I can heal my moods
and counterattack.
[scream]
-No!
-Now I understand the
Warrior Chief's intention.
-Does your wound hurt?
I wasn't able to have my
meal, so I guess we're even.
But then again,
I'm a Homunculus,
so my wounds are
already healing.
The more time passes,
the greater my advantage.
I'm going to eat you
one piece at a time.
But I'll tear your
entire body apart,
making it easier
for me to feast.
-The reason I'm here is so
that terrible day will never
be repeated again.
I must kill all the Homunculi.
BRAVO: I should
probably tell you this.
-What?
-There's not much
difference from how
we prefer our meat to the way
the Homunculi choose theirs.
The younger and fresher it is,
the tastier and more tender
it is.
Or so they claim.
So when they form a
group and take action,
that's what they look for.
They tend to target
schools as prime locations
for securing their food.
Ginsei Academy is an
irresistible target.
It has a whole dormitory
full of sleeping livestock.
-So then enrolling Tokiko in the
school was a preemptive move.
-Rather, a last ditch effort.
Seven years ago, we
Alchemist Warriors
were a day late
and a dollar short,
and ended up sacrificing an
entire elementary school.
We must not repeat that
tragedy ever again.
-Not just in the schools.
-Hm?
-Not just my little sister
and my friends, either.
I'll protect all people
from the Homunculi.
-Well, in that case you
must first get stronger.
And that's my responsibility.
I will have no mercy.
Prepare yourself.
-All right, I'm ready.
Let's do it, Bravo.
BRAVO AND KAZUKI: Buso Renkin!
JINNAI: Oh, it-- it hurts.
-Don't make me laugh.
There's no way a monster should
feel something like pain.
-No, it's true.
It really does hurt.
-Tell me where the LXE base
is, and who the members are.
-I'll talk, I'll talk.
Please just stop already!
[groaning] You've really done
it this time, little girl.
I will make you pay!
-I'll make things
easier if you talk.
But if you don't--
[scream]
-It hurts.
It hurts!
[sigh]
PAPILLON: If you
don't talk, you'll
suffer the torments of
hell before you die?
When you talk like that,
it's hard to distinguish
who is the monster,
and who is the human.
-Papillon.
-No, no, no.
Papillon.
You must put more love into it.
-Kazuki's not
going to like this,
but I kill all
Homunculi in my path.
-Oh?
Ha ha!
-A decoy.
-Please tell Kazuki
this message.
With this, I'll get stronger.
And if he doesn't get
stronger this time around,
then he won't be able to
protect poor little Tokiko.
-Don't press your luck.
Wake up.
Are you all right?
-What happened?
[yawning]
-I don't know why, but I'm
feeling this sense of guilt.
-I feel kinda happy.
With a hint of embarrassment.
It's a good feeling,
nonetheless.
-Tokiko, so soft,
such smooth skin.
-What's up?
Hi, I'm Kazuki.
-My head hurts.
BOY: Why am I so tired?
-Besides the fact that
they were very sleepy,
there doesn't seem to be
any other aftereffect.
They should have no recollection
of what went on last night.
-Bravo, Tokiko.
Very well done.
-But Papillon got a
hold of the Kakugane.
I'm sorry, Warrior Chief.
-Don't apologize.
It's my fault for
overlooking the transmitter
in the first place.
-Huh?
-This training is extremely
rough on a normal boy
like Kazuki.
He has a long road ahead of him.
I wonder how long
he's going to last.
-I have no doubt that
Kazuki will get through it.
But I
-Huh?
-I just-- I still
don't want him moving
any closer to a world of battle.
So I won't let any
enemy near him.
I'm prepared and willing
to do my own fighting.
And I'm ready to take his
share whenever it calls for it.
-Maybe I got her a
little too worked up.
She's more dangerous
now than she was before.
Although it's inevitable that
some warriors fall in battle,
it is harder when
they are so young.
I must avoid that,
whatever the cost.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Last
night ended without incident,
but it was luck.
If one thing went slightly
wrong thing then--
I have no intention of seeing
that site sight ever again.
I have to kill the Homunculi.
I must kill all the enemies.
[bell ringing]
[snoring]
-Huh?
But on, Bravo!
Huh?
-Good morning.
Better hurry.
You'll be late for homeroom.
KAZUKI: Huh?
Oh, uh, right.
Thanks.
Uh, and who are you?
[giggle]
[theme music]
TOKIKO: I would
never have imagined
the LXE making an attack
in such a bold way.
Two Homunculi attack Kazuki.
Those two are twin siblings.
Who are they?
Next time, The Hayasaka Twins,
I'll Splatter Your Guts!
-Hey, there.
This is Mahiro Muto
with another round
of our smashing
seminar of Buso Renkin.
For our third presentation,
we have Captain Bravo's Buso
Renking, the Silver Skin.
Captain Bravo is
the mysterious guy
who suddenly appeared to
become the manager of our dorm
at Ginsei Academy.
He's known as the
Warrior Chief, which
is a very high ranking
Alchemist Warrior.
His real name is a secret,
because it's cooler that way.
That just makes no sense.
Anyway, he seems like
a reliable old man--
uh, I mean young guy--
and together with Tokiko
and Kazuki, fights
to protect us.
Captain Bravo's Buso
Renkin is the Silver Skin.
That weird uniform he wears
is really a metal jacket.
In other words, a
protective suit.
It can completely shut out
any sort of powerful attack
by hardening itself into metal.
And by the way, not only
can it deflect physical
attacks, but also
chemical weapons, as well.
-Wow!
That's incredible.
He's like a walking
bomb shelter.
Well, maybe that's a bit off.
But anyway, even if the
Silver Skin gets damaged,
it can always instantly
repair itself back to normal.
That is impenetrable.
Unfortunately, the
Silver Skin itself
has absolutely no
offensive power.
But that's OK, since Bravo's
weapon is his own body itself,
which has been
trained to the limits.
He's so strong, he can defeat
a Homunculus bare-handed.
With his iron first
and silver skin,
Bravo is absolutely invincible!
They can bring on
whatever the enemies have,
because Captain
Bravo can take them!
But please, tell us
your real name, already.
Okie Dokie.
Tune in next time!