NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
[heavy breathing]
KAZUKI: Where are they?
I really hope they're
both all right.
What's that?
Captain Bravo?
-It's time to settle
our score, Kazuki Muto.
KAZUKI: Hey, what are
you talking about, Bravo?
I mean really, look at me.
I think I look pretty
human right now.
BRAVO: One doesn't become
like Victor at once.
There are stages, and you
are still at stage one.
If my calculations are
correct, your transformation
will be complete
in about six weeks.
By the end of the summer
you will be just like Victor
a monster whose mere existence
brings death and destruction
to all around it.
Before that happens,
you must be disposed of.
That is my new mission.
-Bravo.
-You were killed
by a Homunculus.
The life that Warrior
Tokiko gave you
should never have
been given to anyone.
You must be killed once
again to set things right.
-Bravo!
-Kazuki Muto must
be re-exterminated.
-Say it isn't so, Bravo.
Please tell me you're
kidding, Bravo.
Just say it.
It's a lie!
Lie, lie, lie, lie!
You are lying!
-Food good or for
evil, there is no shame
in holding to your beliefs
until the very end.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
The same words
he used when he recruited
me as a Warrior.
-My mission is to save
as many people as I can.
And to do that I'm even willing
to kill a fellow Warrior if I
need to.
I would even become evil itself.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
So it's true.
The man standing before me
really is Captain Bravo.
-Now, will you law down
your life willingly?
Kazuki.
-I understand.
But not now!
I won't give up just yet.
I can't.
Don't you see that those
are the same words that
encouraged me to become
an Alchemist Warrior?
Believing in my own
convictions, like you?
If six weeks is all I have
left as a human being,
then I'm going to pursue my
convictions to the very end!
Buso Renkin!
-Let's end this now.
-Yes.
I'll triumph and end it here.
[shout]
-Huh?
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Where are you, Kazuki?
Where are you?
[groan]
-Tokiko!
-I've got to search for Kazuki.
I'm concerned.
Where could he be?
He couldn't have gone far.
Huh?
-Come on.
-Thanks, Gota.
[shout]
-Huh?
-No!
[shout]
-Comet Bravo Kick!
-What was that?
-I think it came
from over there.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Kazuki.
[shouting]
-Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
What about you?
How's your shoulder?
-It's all right.
It's really not a big deal.
-By the sound of things,
they should be close.
-Yeah, they must be.
-Kazuki!
-What's going on?
I thought he was battling
Warrior Chief Hiwatari.
-After them!
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Captain Bravo?
[scream]
[shout]
-I didn't expect his
opponent to be Captain Bravo.
-Actually, he may stand a
better chance against Bravo
than Hiwatari.
That is, of course, if
we can catch up to them.
-Yeah, but do you
really think there's
a way to defeat Captain Bravo?
-There is.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): I must
breach his Silver Skin.
-And I will.
-Very impressive strategy.
And yet, it's been in vain.
Very impressive strategy.
[groan]
BRAVO: You grow stronger
the more you fight.
That is why I have to
finish you here and now.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
Silver Skin Reverse.
[shout]
KAZUKI: Gota!
-Just as you suspected, Tokiko.
Even the Silver Skin can't
be precisely controlled
from a distance.
-If you could control
it, you wouldn't
need to wear it at all.
You'd just simply manipulate
it as an automaton
and have it fight for you.
The most you can do is
activate it and launch it.
Isn't that correct?
-That means if you force
your way into it the way
I just did right
now, then the Silver
Skin won't reach its target.
The same thing would
happen even if you
launched the one you're wearing.
My Motor Gears are faster
than your Silver Skin.
-Silver Skin Reverse
will no longer
be effective in this battle.
-Warrior Tokiko,
Warrior Gota, have
you no regrets about the
actions you have chosen?
-None.
-I see.
Then both of you step aside.
Once this battle is
over, I will do my best
to see that you return
to the Alchemist Army
-I'm not interested
in going back.
Not without Kazuki.
Please listen.
We are not acting
on blind faith.
We do have leads.
-Newton Apple Academy for Girls.
-If you know about it, then
give us a little bit more time.
Give Kazuki a chance.
-Even if your actions are
not based on blind faith,
they amount to just a
faint glimmer in the dark.
I cannot risk so many people's
lives on such a tiny ray
of hope.
-Warrior Chief!
-For 100 years, The Alchemist
Army has been pursuing Victor.
My presence here
represents the conclusion
of those hundred years.
There is no other
end but extermination
for those who have
exchanged their lives
for the black Kakugane.
-The Silver Skin can
be torn by an impact
greater than its strength.
That's a fact.
But its regenerative power
far exceeds the speed
of its destruction, and can
prevent a followup attack.
In that case, if the
attack is executed
at a speed that will exceed
the regenerative force--
use this, Kazuki, and
turn into a Victor.
Double Buso Renkin,
plus Victor power.
This is the only way to break
through the Silver Skin.
-No.
If I do that, the energy
drain will engage.
It won't be like that time
at Ginsei Academy, where
there were so many
people around.
-Kazuki--
-I have no doubt that this
could be very harmful to
and Gota, Tokiko.
It could threaten
both your lives.
-What are you saying?
You're giving up
a chance to win?
Don't worry about me.
I made my decision.
-If that's what Tokiko wants,
then I don't mind, either.
-I'm sorry, but I
don't want that.
I want to protect people.
All people.
That's why I became an Alchemist
Warrior in the first place.
So even if I have
to lose this battle,
at least I didn't resort
to harming my friends.
That's my belief.
-Warrior Chief, do you
still intend to kill Kazuki?
Even after you crushed
that single ray of hope,
do you mean to tell me that
you would still kill him?
Warrior Chief, please answer me!
Please answer me, Captain Bravo!
-It's OK, Tokiko.
Neither Captain
Bravo nor I regret
the actions we have taken.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Kazuki.
[shout]
-Huh?
-Silver Skin, Another Type.
Reverse.
[scream]
-Silver Skin, Reverse.
-He's using the Double
Straight on him.
-This is my answer,
Warrior Tokiko.
I will eliminate
Kazuki and defeat
Victor to fulfill my duty as
Warrior Chief Captain Bravo.
-Warrior Chief!
-And once I finish,
I shall end my life
as Mamoru Sakimori, the
criminal responsible for killing
his subordinate.
Kazuki, you won't
have to die alone.
KAZUKI: That's not right.
You can't be serious,
Captain Bravo.
[shout]
-Get ready, Captain Bravo!
I am going to defeat you!
I will win.
I will win, and I'm not
going to let you die.
Energy, full blast!
-Very well.
[shouting]
-Kazuki!
[scream]
-Breach.
Breach.
Breach!
TOKIKO: No hesitation.
No doubt.
He just simply pushed
himself forward
with all his strength and
spirit, and pierced through it.
-You have a strong will to
protect those precious to you.
You threw yourself regardless of
your own safety to save Tokiko.
You defeated Papillon
despite the pain
that it would cause you,
just to prevent more victims.
You pushed your wounded
body to its limits
to save Ouka and Shusui, and
fought with all your might
to protect your friends, your
sister, and the other students
at your school.
You exhibit your
true, full power
at times when you are
trying to protect others.
It's that strong
will that drives
you to protect those
precious to you.
I always knew there would come
a day when you would surpass me,
and that day has come.
Warrior Kazuki.
-Warrior Chief.
-Warrior Tokiko.
-Yes?
-Take everyone and head directly
for Newton Apple Academy
for Girls.
-Warrior Chief.
-I too have decided to gamble
on that tiny ray of hope.
-Thank you very much, sir!
BRAVO (VOICEOVER):
Kazuki has the potential
to do far more good
than I ever will.
I cannot let his life
be wasted in vain.
-So he managed to survive, huh?
A stubborn fellow, isn't he?
[theme music]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Entrusting us
with the hope for the
future, Captain Bravo
sacrifices himself.
These lives that you protected
will not go to waste.
We'll find that
tiny ray of hope.
Next time, Gone Into Flame.
I'll splatter your guts.
-Mahiro Muto's Buso
Renkin seminar.
Hi everyone!
This is Mahiro Muto!
Here is another
exciting introduction
to a Buso Renkin
from yours truly.
For our seventh round,
we have the Motor Gears.
When we all went to
the beach this summer,
this mysterious guy made
quite a cool entrance.
Who is he?
As it turned out, he's Tokiko's
junior and the newest Warrior
in the Alchemist Army.
But wouldn't you
agree that it was
kind of necessary to make
such a dramatic and mysterious
entrance?
Oh!
And check this.
He seems to be madly
in love with Tokiko!
Like she means
everything to him.
Oh boy.
Does that mean my
big brother now
has competition
for her affection?
A man from Tokiko's past?
Oh, my big brother
had better shape up.
But I guess Kazuki doesn't
really have to worry about it,
since they already live in
their own love universe,
so it doesn't matter who
tries to come between them.
Oh!
Silly me!
I forgot to introduce
the guy himself.
His name is Gota
Nakamura, and in many ways
he's a very unfortunate
human being.
Wow.
I kinda feel bad for him.
Anyway, this poor,
unfortunate guy's
Buso Renkin is called
the Motor Gears.
They are two
circular-shaped rings
called the chakram,
an Indian weapon
that works like a boomerang.
Gota inputs the speed, angle,
and number of rotations
through his bioelectricity
into the Moto Gears
and throws them as an attack.
Hiya!
Oh, that sounded good.
Anyway, he can also attach
them his hands and feet.
For example, he can attach them
to his fists and then punch!
That's called
Knuckle Duster mode.
He can also attach
them to his ankles
and move like an inline skater.
Woosh!
That one is called
Skywalker mode.
And there's also one more,
the Marine Diver mode,
which he uses like a
propeller under water.
Cool.
Huh?
Oh.
By the way.
Of all the Buso
Renkin, the Motor Gears
ranked the lowest
in terms of power.
[sigh] Didn't I say he
was kind of unfortunate?
But I remember Tokiko did
say Gota's wits compensate
for his lack of power.
Right?
So don't you ever, ever give up.
Do your best, Gota Nakamaura.
Go, go, Gota!
All right.
That's it for now.
Okie dokie.
Until next time.