NARRATOR: A supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: The all out
attack on Victor has begun.
The Alchemist Warriors made
full use of their Buso Renkins
and tried to corner Victor.
But Victor evolved
into his third stage
and showed the Alchemist Army
the true extent of his powers.
Meanwhile, Kazuki and
the others arrived
at Newton Apple
Academy for Girls.
They came upon
the white Kakugane
that could restore Kazuki
be back to his human form.
However--
FEMALE VOICE: It'll
be a few more days
before the white
Kakugane is completed.
Until then, think carefully
before you make your decision.
-It must be quite a
lot for you to handle,
but you should
consider yourself lucky
since you still have a choice.
-Do you have a pencil?
I forgot my pencil.
-Aw.
I just hate going
to summer school.
It's supposed to
be summer vacation.
Huh?
-Oh, there they are.
-The bell's already
rung, and you guys
are still taking your time?
-Hey.
It's been a while!
-Come on, let's go.
-Kazuki!
Tokiko!
-If we don't hurry, we'll
be late for home room.
-So, how'd it go?
Any new developments
between you two?
-Huh?
What do you mean by that?
-Isn't it about time you
made it clear to her?
I'm sure Tokiko feels--
-Argh.
Stop.
Stay where you are.
I'll splatter your guts!
You guys are so annoying.
-They look happy.
-I'd say they are!
-You would think they didn't
have a worry in the world.
-What's there really
to worry about?
Kazuki hasn't done
anything wrong in his life.
He should just return to being
human with great dignity.
-You're right.
Not only has he
done nothing wrong.
He's also protected this school
and the city again and again.
But--
BRAVO: And because
of the kind of boy
he is, that's why he won't
be able to just leave
Victor like that in the end.
-He really is a very strong boy.
-Yes, he is.
It's almost as if he were
born to become a Warrior,
and nothing else.
He's only going to become
stronger in mind and body.
-Hm.
-But-- we shouldn't forget,
he is still a 17-year-old high
school kid.
-So it's true!
You've returned!
Welcome back!
-Hi, Mahiro!
I'm back!
-Tokiko, you're
back, you're back!
Oh, yeah.
Welcome back, Kazuki.
-Hey.
-Now, now.
-It may not look like
it, but she was really
worried about you.
-So--
-You came back in one piece.
That must mean your mission
was successful, right, Kazuki?
-That's right.
-Well, listen, guys.
We're only gonna have
school until noon today.
So what do you say we
hang out afterwards?
-That's a great idea.
Kazuki, you and Tokiko are
gonna come with us, right?
-Of course.
So, where are we going?
-I'd love to go to
the amusement park!
-Hey, good call, Mahiro.
-What about the pool?
-Sounds good, too.
-But the girls at
the pool won't be
wearing their school
swimwear, Daihama.
-Kazuki!
-Something like bowling
could be a lot of fun, too.
-How about a Go parlor?
-The amusement
park's a better idea.
-You really love amusement
parks, don't you, Okakura?
-As a matter of fact,
I love them, too.
-Me too!
-What do you mean by that?
-The matter is obvious.
After we win this ongoing
battle against Victor,
the re-extermination of
Kazuki Muto will be next.
And that's all there is to it.
What are you gonna do?
-Warrior Chief Hiwatari.
-What is it?
-The seventh and eighth
units have almost
been completely wiped out.
An order has been issues to
withdraw the second class
combat deployment immediately.
We've been ordered to back up
Buster Baron with his attacks,
instead.
-All right.
That means all of you ladies.
So you'd better get
yourselves ready.
Busujima, you'll be
returning to headquarters.
-Hold it.
Are you saying that you're going
to use Kazuki to defeat Victor,
then you're just going to
kill him like he's nothing?
-And what are you
gonna do about it, huh?
You know what?
Discussing this with you is
simply a waste of my time.
Right now what we
gotta do is focus
on killing the enemy that's
right in front of our eyes.
Understand?
Besides, ultimately
it doesn't matter
which one we end up
taking care of first.
If we had killed that brat back
then when we had the chance,
then things wouldn't have
gotten this complicated.
Absurd, isn't it?
Well, that's just
the world we live in.
-All right, then.
I will concentrate on the
enemy before my eyes for now,
but whatever actions I
need to take after that,
I will decide when
the time comes.
-Glad you finally
see things my way.
Here you go.
SHISUI (VOICEOVER): Kazuki.
I won't give up on you.
-Can you believe we have
homework on the first day?
-Hey Tokiko, Kazuki's
taking a little longer,
so we're gonna go on ahead.
You mind waiting for him?
-We'll be at the station, OK?
-I guess I don't
mind, but wouldn't it
be better if we all
just go together?
-All right!
We're counting on you!
-See you later!
-Oh, hey, wait.
Hold on a second.
[sigh]
-You came back in one piece!
That must mean your mission
was successful, right Kazuki?
That's right?
I completely lied to them.
GOTA: Well, isn't that
better than making
them worry unnecessarily?
-Gota!
-I was worried that perhaps
Tokiko was being treated
like an outcast at school,
but your younger sister
and your friends
are good people.
Whatever choice you
make in the end,
as long as you promise
not to hurt Tokiko,
then I'll do whatever
I can to help you out.
You have my word on that.
If we are protecting
the same thing,
I'd say that makes us allies.
-Gota.
-I won't be shaking your hand.
We may be allies, but we're
still rivals for Tokiko's hand.
-Hm.
PAPILLON: So, what makes
that girl so great, anyway?
-Huh?
-I don't get it.
It defies all explanation.
-Chouno!
-Hi.
-You're here.
I was wondering why
I hadn't seen you
since we left the
Girls' Academy.
So tell me, where have
you been this whole time?
-In my secret lab, of
course, conducting research
on the white Kakugane.
-What?
You're planning on making
another white Kakugane?
-My ultimate goal is to
defeat the human Kazuki Muto
while achieving
my highest power.
And for that to happen, a
white Kakugane is essential.
-But, remember what
Alexandria said?
-How long would it take to
create another black Kakugane
from scratch, and then alter
it into a white Kakugane?
ALEXANDRIA: The
process for creating
a black Kakugane was
lost 100 years ago.
Unfortunately, it would be just
about impossible for my aged
brain to duplicate
one from scratch.
-Hm.
When I was still a human
being, every doctor who saw me
told me that my
days were numbered.
But, as you can see, I'm
still alive and kicking.
A choice isn't something
that just falls from the sky
and is given to you.
You have to create it yourself.
Muto, no matter what
your decision is,
I'm not giving up on
settling our score.
KAZUKI: Yeah.
I know.
Hey, Tokiko!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
-What took you so long?
Everything OK?
-Huh?
Oh, I'm fine.
Where is everyone?
-Well, they all went ahead.
But if we hurry,
we can catch up.
-Oh, really?
Then let's go!
It's pretty hot.
-Huh?
Oh, yeah.
Kazuki, are you all right?
Given the circumstances,
are you OK?
-I'm fine.
-All right, then.
If you say so, Kazuki.
-Yup.
I'm fine.
Let's go.
-The sky is so blue, isn't it?
-Yeah.
This year is
definitely a hot one.
[scraping]
-Mm.
-Here you go.
Thank you for waiting.
-Thanks.
Here you go.
Enjoy it.
-Uh, thank you.
Uh--
GIRL: Is yours good?
-Mm-hm.
-What is it?
-I was just remembering
how when we were younger,
Mahiro and I used to
eat snow cones all
the time in the summer.
When I was a little
boy, I would always
order melon flavored
syrup, and of course Mahiro
would always get the
strawberry flavor.
But this one time Mahiro
wanted to try the melon flavor,
and so I gave her some.
But it spilled on her dress,
so she started to cry.
And I got flustered, and
I tried to console her.
By the time she stopped
crying, both our shaved ices
had melted.
-It sounds like
you and your sister
have always gotten along, huh?
This is the first
time I've heard
you talk about your
childhood, Kazuki.
-Oh, really?
-I find it rather
refreshing to hear people
talk about their past, you know?
Perhaps because all I
have now is the present.
-What do you mean by that?
-I have no past.
According to the
doctor, it seems
I have partial memory
loss due to trauma.
At least that's what
they say, anyway.
And because of that, all my
past memories are very vague.
All right.
I think that's enough
talk about me for now.
Anyway, that's the way it is.
-I don't know.
Maybe there just isn't a way
to unlock your past after all.
But I would like to see the
future with you, Tokiko.
-Oh.
Yes, I agree.
I also would like to see
the future with you, Kazuki.
-Are you blushing?
-Shut up!
Why do you say things like that?
-Uh--
[groaning]
-Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
MAHIRO: Oh, so this
is where you both are.
-What are you doing here?
You kept us waiting.
-I was worried you two had
run off into the sunset.
-Maybe you should
update your slang.
-We're sorry.
I guess we just got distracted.
-Wait a minute.
Snow cones?
-Hey, let's have some.
-No!
We have to hurry to
the amusement park.
-Whoa, I guess you really
do like amusement parks.
-It just means that
he's still boy at heart.
[laughter]
-Get off my back, will ya?
[screaming]
[laughter]
MAHIRO: Hang on!
-Help me!
-Whoa!
[laughter]
-Too much spinning!
[scream]
[laughter]
-Yeah, yeah.
[scream]
-Okakura?
-Whoa!
Whoa!
-Okakura?
Okakura, are you all right?
-For someone who loves amusement
parks, you're quite a crybaby.
-Let's go on the next one!
-Whoa!
-Come on, Tokiko, let's go.
-No.
I'll skip this one.
I'm gonna take a break.
-Oh, OK.
Well then, Okakura,
Rokumasu, Daihama.
Let's go.
-Yeah!
-Huh?
-Hm.
[scream]
-Okakura?
Wait!
-All right, let's ride
the flying carpet next!
-Hey!
What are you doing?
Wait for us!
-Are we still going with them?
-Yeah, let's go, let's go!
-All right, Tokiko!
You're coming, too!
-Ah--
-Oh, here she comes now.
-Sorry, guys.
Shouldn't we be getting back?
-No!
There's going to be an
after party with karaoke.
-Karaoke?
-That's right.
You're going to have a chance
to hear some of my hot rock n'
roll styling.
You'll love it.
-I've come prepared
with earplugs.
-Wait, why are you
carrying those around?
-How dare you use earplugs
while I'm singing!
[laughter]
-Hey, guys, I'm sorry, but
I think I'm gonna get going.
-Aw, really?
-Why, are you tired?
Are you all right?
-Mm-hm.
-That's probably a smart move.
-What the hell do
you mean by that?
-In that case--
-Hey, wait, Tokiko!
You're coming with
us, aren't you?
-You mustn't leave yet!
-See you later, Kazuki.
-Take it easy.
-Be careful, all right?
-Don't catch cold.
-Sure.
See ya.
[excited chatter]
TOKIKO: No.
Really.
You don't want me to sing.
I promise.
-How it will be used will
be your decision, Kazuki.
-Whatever choice you
decide to make in the end,
I will do anything within my
power to support you, Muto.
But you must promise not
to make Tokiko suffer.
-Muto, no matter what
your decision will be,
I am not giving up on
settling my score with you.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): The thing
is, I know what my decision is.
Deep down, I already knew.
But if I do that, I'll--
I'll protect everyone,
but then who's
going to protect me?
-Kazuki, you all right?
-Tokiko.
What are you doing here?
-This is my special place.
-Oh, that's right.
-It isn't like you to leave
early like that, Kazuki.
Everyone was really
worried about you.
-Oh.
-Huh?
Oh, that's right.
Kazuki.
Look, over there.
-Th haunted factory
behind the school.
-When we met for the first time
there, you tried to protect me.
Thank you.
-Huh?
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
Oh, that's right.
That day.
I jumped in without
even thinking
about what I was doing.
I was simply determined
to protect the girl.
The girl in front of my eyes.
An that desire that I had back
then, it's still with me today.
If anything, it's
gotten stronger.
I want to protect her.
-Huh?
-Tokiko?
I've decided.
But I'm still lacking courage.
-Really?
In that case, then I'll make
up for what you're lacking.
-Thanks.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): It's
as I said that one night.
When you die, I
will die with you.
You and I are of
one mind and body.
[beeping]
[shout]
[theme music]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Staking our final hopes
on one thing alone,
the white Kakugane.
You head on to confront
Victor, but Kazuki, I
will not let you go alone.
Next episode, When You
Die, I'll Die With You.
-Mahiro Muto's Buso
Renkin Seminar.
Hello.
This is Mahiro
Muto, and I'm here
to introduce another
explosive set of Buso Renkin.
Believe it or not,
for our eighth,
we have the whole gang
from the Alchemist Army.
First up is this
guy Genja Ikusabe.
With a name difficult
to pronounce,
it sounds like he
could be a samurai.
Mr. Ikusabe weilds the Cross
Spear Buso Renkin Gekisen.
Its special property
is rapid regeneration.
In other words, even if
the spear and the wielder
are damaged, it
will automatically
repair itself in an instant.
Then we have Shinobu Negoro.
Mr. Negoro wields the
Ninja Sword Buso Renkin,
Secret Trail.
He says with this, he
can cut through objects
to enter and exit
subspace at will.
He comes out of the
darkness in stealth.
Now that's a ninja.
Uh, by the way,
what's a subspace?
Uh-- anyway, next we
have Rintaro Inukai.
Mr. Inukai's Buso
Renkin is a dog!
Well, not exactly.
It's a military dog style Buso
Renkin called Killer Rabies.
But, well, I guess
it still is a dog.
A dog type robot, that is.
And it's way more
amazing than a real dog.
But when it comes to
real dogs, Mr. Inukai
is totally afraid of them!
Ah, it makes no sense.
Oh!
And then there's
Madoku Maruyama.
The name and looks give
the impression of a woman,
but he is a full fledged man.
Mr. Maruyama uses
a floating mine,
an explosive Balloon Buso
Renkin called the Bubble Cage.
Each time the grotesque faced
balloons surround themselves
around the target and explode,
the number of balloons
increases and presses
down on the target!
And then there's
Hanaka Busujima.
She's really very cute, but
thanks to that bulky Gas Mask
Buso Renkin, called
Aerial Operator,
you can't see
Hanaka's true face.
With her Buso Renkin,
she can mix and create
all sorts of gas.
But I still wanna see her face!
And next, could it be
Bravo's girlfriend?
Or, sort of.
Maybe not.
Who knows?
Well, her name is
Chitose Tateyama.
Miss Chitose's Buso Renkin
is the Hermes Drive.
Taking the shape of a
radar, it can locate anyone,
as long as she knows them.
Oh, and on top of
that, it also gives her
the ability to teleport.
And then there's Warrior
Chief Sekima Hiwatari.
His Buso Renkin
is a napalm bomb,
called Blaze of Glory,
capable of creating
an instantaneous maximum
temperature of 10,000 degrees!
It can burn everything
in its path.
Or so he says.
But 10,000 degrees!
Oh!
Well, it must mean
it's very hot, right?
And that's not all!
There's his Pyro
Fusion, where he
can merge with that
super hot flame
to nullify the
opponent's attacks.
I'm saying this without really
knowing too much about it,
though.
Anyway, last but not least, we
have the Great Warrior Chief
Shosei Sakaguchi.
He sure doesn't go by the
title of Great Warrior
Chief for nothing.
His Buso Renkin is the
giant robot Buster Baron.
What part of that
is Buso Renkin?
That's just way over the top.
The Buster Baron can even power
up other peoples' Buso Renkin,
and use it for itself!
So, that's all the Buso Renkin
from the Alchemist Army.
Well, next time is our final
one, so please tune in!
Okie dokie!