[theme music]
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
It's a dream.
It's got to be a dream.
-Behind you!
-This wasn't supposed to happen.
[shouting]
-Shut up, Kazuki!
-What's the matter, Kazuki?
-Can't you at least try to be
quiet at this time of night?
[groaning]
-Something just killed me.
-Are you still asleep?
-I'll avenge my death, dang it!
BOY: What?
Have you lost your mind?
[shouting]
-What's up with them?
They're being so noisy.
-What's going on?
-Seems like some sophomore
year guy is acting up.
[sigh]
-I know that voice.
It's my big brother.
-He seems to be doing OK.
He should be fine, at
least for the time being,
thanks to the power of alchemy.
KAZUKI: Good morning.
-Good morning, Kazuki.
-Hey there.
-I heard the you were
half asleep last night
and went on a crazy
rampage back in the dorm.
-Whoa, word travels fast!
So who's the snitch?
-It was me.
-Okakura!
-Look at this.
I didn't even have
to say anything.
These wounds say it all.
-Wowie.
Who'd have thought
that the learn at home
karate I've been doing since
my first year of junior high
would result in
something so lethal.
That's pretty damn cool.
-Shut up, you idiot.
Apologize!
-Sorry.
-That's better.
DAIHAMA: You sure gave us a
hard time last night, didn't he,
Rokumasu?
-Yeah, that's right.
If Daihama hadn't been
there to stop you,
you might still be
fighting Okakura.
-Sorry about that.
-So tell us, what was
your dream about anyway?
It was weird.
Not only scary, but painful too.
On top of that, I can still
remember every detail.
-In the abandoned building
behind the school?
-You mean the haunted factory?
-Right.
There was a girl I didn't
know wearing a school uniform,
and I saved her as
she was about to be
attacked by some
strange creature.
-That is weird.
-But I got killed instead.
-You mean you didn't beat it?
-Really?
-Hey there, big brother!
-Oh, hi Mahiro.
-Oh yeah. she's a freshman,
starting today isn't she?
-Congratulations, Mahiro.
-The uniform really suits you.
-Really?
I'm glad to hear that.
To be honest, the reason I
actually came to this school
is because I love
this uniform so much.
-Hey, so do I. As
a matter of fact,
the only reason I came to
this school is because I love
the girls' unifo--
-Enough fooling around.
Let's go.
[excited chatter]
-Uh, so my big brother
likes this uniform too?
-Kazuki, you're
confusing your sister.
MITA: Hey, you over there.
Why aren't you caring your
school designated bag?
-Um, I'm sorry.
I sort of couldn't find it
when I got up this morning.
-So, you lost it.
Where were you after
school yesterday?
-Well, uh, let me think.
Uh.
-Hm.
Well, I'll make an
exception this time,
Kazuki Muto, Class
2B, but I'll need
you to report to the teachers'
room during lunch break.
-But what for?
-Back talk will
not be tolerated.
Understood?
-Yes sir, I understand.
MITA (VOICEOVER): I found you.
OKAKURA: Mita's sure been
acting strange lately.
-What do you mean, lately?
I always thought he was
the weirdest teacher
in the entire school
to begin with.
-Thanks for waiting, guys.
-Hey, Kazuki.
So what did Mita have to say?
-You're never gonna
believe what he said.
TOGETHER: Pull out the weeds
in the school's back court?
-That's just plain weird.
What's up with that, huh?
-Yeah, why would he ask you
to do something like that
all by yourself?
-More importantly, why
didn't you just say no?
-Well, I did, but then he said
he would make Mahiro do it,
so I had no choice.
MAHIRO: What?
No way.
That's terrible.
I'm going to protest.
-Mahiro, wait.
You can drink this.
-Can I really?
-Pulling weeds and
green juice are
both to celebrate my
little sister's admission
to this school.
DAIHAMA: She's
really drinking that.
OKAKAURA: They're
definitely related.
-So, do you want us
to give you a hand?
-Yeah.
I wanna help you too.
-No, it's cool.
I'm sure I can manage
pulling weeds on my own.
But I'll probably
be late, so please
be sure to save me some dinner
for when I get home, all right?
-OK, I'll do that!
[bell chiming]
-First bell.
come on.
I guess we should get going.
[phone beeping]
-Huh?
A text message?
Wonder who it's from.
What is this supposed to mean?
-Such a peaceful town.
But I'm sure they're
lurking somewhere out there,
-Whew!
I'm finally finished.
Man.
The school sure is
creepy at night.
The haunted factory, up
over in the back hills.
Things sure have been
weird here since yesterday.
I should just check
out and go home.
MITA: Where do you
think you're going?
OKAKURA: Hey, where you going?
-Oh, hi there.
Well, I'm going to
pick up my big brother.
-What a nice sister you are.
-I was thinking I'd
offer to help him,
if he hasn't finished
with all those weeds.
-Have you finished with
the work I asked you to do.
-More or less.
-More or less, huh?
Well, that really
doesn't matter.
-That's my bag.
Where'd you find it?
-The abandoned factory
on the back hill.
It was left behind
last night by someone
who interrupted my dinner.
Meaning you.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
What's going on?
-How can you be alive?
I was sure I killed you when I
skewered your heart last night.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): This
must be a dream too.
If not, I couldn't
be alive right now.
-Doesn't matter.
If you survived that, then this
time I'll kill you for good!
-If it's not a dream, and last
night wasn't a dream, then--
[phone ringing]
-Who's this?
-I'll be there in three minutes.
Just hang on until then.
KAZUKI (ON PHONE):
What's happening?
What is that thing?
And who are you anyway?
What exactly is going on here?
WOMAN (ON PHONE): It's
not easy to talk and run
at the same time, so I'll
give you the quick version.
-Yes, please do.
WOMAN (ON PHONE): That thing
is called a Homunculus.
It's a creature that hides in
people, transforms into people,
and eats people.
-It eats people?
-Yes.
I followed that
thing to this town,
and then got you involved.
-I'm involved?
What do you mean I'm involved?
How?
WOMAN (ON PHONE):
I see you still
haven't remembered
everything, huh?
-Well, what am I
supposed to remember?
WOMAN (ON PHONE): Anyway.
Don't stop.
Keep running.
In order to hide
their existence,
they never let a witness live.
They'll chase you down forever.
Once you get involved,
there is no way out.
-Whoa, you scared me!
What's with that
look on your face?
-Mahiro.
What are you doing here?
-Well, you were running late,
so I came to check up on you.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): Oh no.
I got her involved.
-Run, Mahiro!
I'll figure out a
way to hold him off.
-What are you talking about
What's the matter, big brother?
Big brother!
-Get out of here, now!
-It's a bit difficult to move in
this form on an empty stomach.
But this should
make up for the meal
that I missed out on
eating last night.
-Give her back!
Give her back!
She's got nothing
to do with this.
Give her back!
-No need to get carried away.
This body was created
by alchemy and will not
relent to anything but
the power of alchemy.
-What do you mean,
the power of alchemy?
WOMAN: Can you hear me?
The reason you
died is because you
got involved without being
aware of the consequences
of your actions.
However.
You attempted to save
my life last night.
Your actions have
piqued my interest.
This is a Kakugane.
It is a paranormal alloy
forged by concentrating
the essence of alchemy.
It functions in response to the
deepest part of the human mind.
The human instinct.
It will awaken the
survival instinct
as a substitute for the heart.
You will regain the
power to live again.
And at the same time,
you'll obtain another power.
That is the power to fight.
Activated by human
instinct, it will give you
the strength you
need to do battle.
That is the true
power of the Kakugane.
-It looks like you don't
know when to quit, do you?
You already should've
died last night.
-You will give back Mahiro.
-Keep dreaming.
You'll be eaten up and
joining your little sister.
-You monster!
-You fool!
You still don't get it, do you?
Huh?
Get out of my way.
-Buso Renkin.
Valkyrie Skirt!
-You again.
It's you!
You're the one from last night.
Death scythe Buso Renkin!
So that can only mean one thing!
You're an Alchemist Warrior!
-Mahiro!
I remember.
Last night on the
way home from school,
I looked up and saw a light
on in the haunted factory,
and when I went there, you
were about to be eaten by Mita.
-No.
I just pretended
to be defenseless
so I could lure him out.
-You're kidding?
-No, it's true.
-So I died because of
a misunderstanding?
That is just so lame!
Mahiro, are you OK?
-She's probably doing
much better than you are.
There's really nothing
wrong with her.
-Thank goodness.
I feel a lot better
now that I know that.
-You really are strange.
Both last night
and just now, you
told me you were full
of fear and pain,
yet you appear courageous.
Well, whichever it
is, you certainly
have piqued my interest.
KAZUKI: Here it is.
It really is in the dictionary.
-Alchemy.
An integrated science technology
which spread all across Europe
before the time
of the modern age.
The original goal was
to change lead to gold,
or to create an elixir
for eternal life.
These attempts were
not successful,
but would become the
foundation for modern science.
What's the matter?
You've got a weird
look on your face.
-It's-- It's nothing.
I was born this way.
-Oh really?
I'm very sorry to hear that.
-Huh?
Wait.
Hold on a minute.
You just said that
it wasn't successful?
-As far as anyone who
reads this is concerned.
Alchemy did have two
paranormal successes
that were incomprehensible
to normal people.
They were Homunculi
and Buso Renkin.
-Homunculi and Buso Renkin?
What do you mean?
-Homunculi are the byproducts
of research on artificial life.
Buso Renkin is the result of
tactical munitions development.
However, they were both
just too dangerous.
In the end, they were hidden
from the general public
and were left in
the hands of those
who truly understood
the powers of alchemy.
Unfortunately, many have slipped
through the hands of those
responsible and are scattered
throughout the world,
and now they prey upon humans
under the dark of night.
-The haunted factory.
It's a hideout
for the Homunculi.
I must go defeat
the rest of them.
Buso Renkin.
-I wanna go too!
If there's anything I
can do to help, then--
-Just stay away.
The reason I gave
you the Kakugane
was not because I
wanted you to fight,
but because I felt that your
life was a life worth saving.
I told you about the
Homunculi and Buso Renkin
so you could properly grasp
the situation and deal
with any circumstances
you encounter.
Battle is my mission alone.
-But still, I--
-Just stay away.
What about your sister?
I want you to think about that.
When she wakes up from
her terrifying nightmare,
how would she feel
if she found herself
alone in the health
office at night?
Let me try to make this as
clear as possible for you.
What you decide now will
determine your future.
Return to the world you know
or enter a world of battle.
I don't need to tell
you which world it
is you belong to, right?
I've no intention of
involving you any further.
Just stay away.
You must not come.
You should just go
home, with your sister.
-I'm not sure why,
but I feel like I've
been through a very
scary experience.
-What can I do to wake her up?
She probably just needs some
medicine to wake her up.
Maybe this'll work.
Or this.
-Stop it!
You're scaring me!
Oh, that's right.
I fell in the schoolyard
and I bumped my head.
It's so cold in here.
-Well, it's because you're
not wearing a jacket.
Here you go.
-Thanks, brother.
-So, Mahiro.
How tall are you these days?
-Um, well, I guess
I'm about 5 foot 3.
-Really?
I see.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): Her
shoulders sure seemed small.
-Thanks again, Kazuki.
I'm better now.
Let's hurry back
to the dorm, OK?
Big brother?
-All right.
Are you ready to go, then?
-Ah huh.
-Let's run, Mahiro.
Quick, come on!
-No!
But why?
Why?
-I'll splatter your guts!
-It's a woman!
-Think again.
It looks like you're the prey.
WOMAN (VOICEOVER):
There's too many of them.
This is more than
just a simple hideout.
-This must be the woman Mita
talked about last night.
-That's the last one.
-I see.
So you're The alchemist Warrior.
The Buso Renkin expert who's
been chosen from among those
who truly understand alchemy.
But do you really think you
can just much march in here
and win by yourself?
-I always fight alone.
Come on.
-This should be fun!
-I've got her, Mr. Saruwatari!
-He hid inside a corpse!
-It's tough by yourself,
isn't it, Alchemist Warrior?
-Let me go!
Filthy!
[laughter]
[shout]
-Huh?
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
It is that instinct
that actives it and gives
you the strength to fight.
That is the true
power of the Kakugane.
It transforms their
dormant fighting strength
into a weapon like no other.
Control, determination,
and roar!
It's called--
-Buso Renkin!
-I'm back.
-Hi.
Welcome back, Mahiro.
-Hey, so where' Kazuki?
-We were together until
we got to the front door.
But then he said he had
something to take care of,
and left.
-And this time of night?
Shouldn't it wait until morning?
-Well, I asked him
that, too, but he
said he absolutely
needed to go now.
[shout]
-What is this?
You'll never be able
to beat my strength.
Do you have any idea
how strong I am?
I didn't think so!
-Pierce through, my Buso Renkin!
-The cloth is
turning into energy!
[scream]
-It's so powerful.
What about your little sister?
-Don't worry about her.
She's safe and sound at home.
I ran full speed for
30 minutes, but I still
have lots of energy--
-It doesn't look that way.
Why did you come?
I warned you not to come here.
-I couldn't choose.
-What are you talking about?
-Mahiro's important
to me, but I just
couldn't leave you
here all by yourself.
-Take a look
underneath your feet.
-Huh?
What-- what is this?
-I told you.
This is how they do things.
It seems this isn't
their normal hideout.
The ones who were here
have been wiped out,
but more of these
monsters are surely
lurking somewhere in town.
-I can't believe it.
More monsters like that
are still out there?
-The situation is worse
than I first thought.
You should not get
involved any further.
-That's all the more
reason I can't back out.
If such things are still
lurking in our town,
Mahiro and the others
will be in danger.
I have the power to
fight that you gave me,
and now I must use it.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): He's acting
differently from last night.
Even though he's
aware of the dangers,
he's still willing to fight.
-Just so you know,
I was telling you
all of this for your own good.
-I understand.
But just so you know, there's
no way I can just stand by
and simply do nothing about it.
I'm going to help you get
rid of these monsters.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Kazuki Muto.
This boy has the qualities of
a virtuous warrior within him.
-Nothing I say to you is going
to change your mind, is it?
-That's right.
-OK.
Got it.
Then you will begin training
as a Warrior Apprentice.
But I don't want you
dying on me ever again.
From now on, you are to
follow my instructions.
Got it?
-I got it.
But you--
-Now what?
-You never told me
what your name is.
-I'm sorry.
I guess I forgot to tell you.
Listen up.
My name is Tokiko.
Tokiko Tsumura.
-Tokiko Tsumura?
[theme music]
TOKIKO: The boy who I've
given the Kakugane to.
His Buso Renkin is powerful,
but he doesn't completely
understand.
Next time, The True
Form Homunculus.
I'll splatter your guts!