NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
-My ears hurt!
-What's that sound?
-The alarm.
He, my friend, has awakened.
-What the--
-Angel Gozen!
-I-- feel weak--
-Suddenly I--
-Chii-chin!
Sally!
What--
[groaning]
-It's like--
-My strength is being
sucked out of me.
DR. BUTTERFLY: This
is how he feeds.
He doesn't bother eating flesh.
That has very poor
absorption efficienty.
He takes away the
life force directly
and transforms it into
energy for himself.
-This is bad, KazukI!
If we don't do
something quickly,
everyone will have their
lives drained out of them!
-I won't let that happen.
No!
DR. BUTTERFLY: Be
quiet, insolent boy.
That line belongs to Dr.
Butterfly, now renamed
Master Butterfly!
Ah!
-There is no need
to follow through
with the order Muto had
made, now, is there?
If you're going to go
along with anything at all,
we should just do it my way.
I got that on my own,
without any help.
However, there is
something I'm still
grateful for, Great Grandfather.
But as for you protecting
me, it's kind of bothersome
that you believe I am that weak.
I don't need your
protection, anyway.
And to prove it, it'll
cost you your life.
-Are you rebelling against me?
Then that means your
death has been ordained.
-Really?
I've already learned the special
property of your Buso Renkin.
It affects the nervous
system and disrupts
one's sense of direction.
You're no match for my
Near Death Happiness.
-You are such a fool.
You've only seen my Buso
Reinkin in a diffused state.
Its power in a concentrated
state is simply unimaginable.
Prepare yourself for the
true power of my Buso Renkin!
I'll crush your mind and spirit,
killing you little by little.
-Before that, I'll
burn you to ashes!
[laughter]
-Someone like you has no chance,
and you want to know why?
Let me explain.
-That may have been true
when we were still humans.
Things are differet now.
Completely different.
My name is Papillon!
And you say it surpasses
both humans and Homunculi.
I was convinced the
humanoid Homunculus
was the ultimate life form.
But now you tell me there's
something even greater.
I've decided.
I'll cast off this
imperfect body of mine,
and flap my wings toward
even greater heights.
Great Grandfather, we are
alike, yet so difficult.
You flutter arround
a dazzling light,
unable to fly high alone.
As far as I'm concerned,
you're no butterfly.
You're just an ugly moth.
-Don't stop, Kazuki!
-I know.
Let's keep moving.
-We have to get up to the
roof as fast as we can.
We cannot waste one second.
-I know!
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
I know, but--
-Kazuki, what is it?
This is--
-My friends.
-Kazuki!
Don't open it, Kazuki.
I know what you're
feeling, but it's important
that we keep moving.
Don't open it.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
If you open that door,
you won't be able to go on.
-I'm sorry.
I just can't-- pass right by.
-Kazuki!
-I thought I heard
a voice out here.
I figured it was you.
-Okakura!
-Are you all OK?
-Yeah.
-What about the
rest of the class?
-Well, everyone should be fine.
-Don't go in there.
Like Daihama said,
everyone's OK.
Don't worry.
-Yeah, but--
-Really.
You don't have to go to the
trouble of looking inside.
There's no need to go in.
-But I--
-With all that happened,
they had a little more
of a frightening
experience than the others,
so they look a bit shaken.
We were just on our way
to the nurses' office.
Really, they're OK.
-But--
-If we're saying we're
OK, then we're OK!
Just shut up and get going.
There are still monsters
out there, right?
Aren't you guys supposed to be
the only ones who can defeat
them?
We're all counting on
you, do you understand?
So for everyone's
sake, listen to me.
-I'll fight.
-All right.
I just knew you'd
say that, buddy.
So go out and kick their butts.
Go fight, and win for all of us!
-Tokiko!
-Huh?
-Please take care
of my big brother.
Sometimes he tends to
push himself too much.
-I know.
OKAKURA: He can be
such a pain sometimes.
DAIHAMA: Oh, well.
That's Kazuki for you.
-We should get going.
-Yeah.
You're right.
We should get these girls
to the nurse-- nurse's--
[groan]
OKAKURA (VOICEOVER): So go
out and kick their butts.
Go fight, and win for all of us!
-Kazuki?
-We're taking a shortcut.
-What?
-You seem to be in quite a
bit of pain, Great, Great
Grandfather.
If you'll tell me about
the man in the flask,
I might find some
compassion, and take you
under my protection.
-Ha ha ha.
-Sarcastic bastard.
Nice choice of words,
considering you've
already made a huge
hole in my emblem mark.
Oh, very well.
I will tell you, and not
because you are my relative,
but because you are a
fellow alchemist striving
for greater heights.
-Hm?
-Victor.
He was originally an alchemist
warrior many years ago.
100 years, to be exact.
He turned into the
third type of being
that surpasses both
humans and Homunculi.
He was pursued by his comrades,
and after a fierce battle,
he sought exile here.
In exchange for sharing his
alchemy knowledge with me,
I promised to restore his
severely wounded body,
regardless of how
long it wold take me.
-I've heard that
whole story already.
It seems you've
gone senile on me.
-Don't rush an old man
telling a complex story.
-Ah?
-For the next hundred
years, my only purpose
was to become the
best alchemist I
could be, in order to
perfect my original creation.
The Restoration Flask.
I also created the LXE
in order to protect him
from the Alchemist Warriors.
-So tell me, why was he
pursued by his comrades?
-I don't know.
Try asking him for yourself.
-What is his ultimate goal?
-I don't know.
Only he can answer that.
-How can I become like him?
-You'll have to figure
that out for yourself.
-What is this, I will tell
you, you stinking old man?
Your complex story didn't
answer anything at all.
-Well, what do you expect?
I am nothing but an ugly moth.
Isn't that what you said?
You see, moths are
attracted to the light,
but it is presumptuous
for a moth
to attempt to touch the light.
As an alchemist and
as a friend, I've
been completely
fascinated by him.
Restoring him is enough
fulfillment for a lifetime.
Mm.
Like a good moth, I
am satisfied to have
been able to fly about
his bright light.
-And how would you ever
expect to become a butterfly
with that attitude?
-Hm.
Don't miss out, Papillon!
-Kazuki?
MASTER BUTTERFLY: If you wish
to truly fly to further heights
as a butterfly, then
don't take your eyes
off the battle that
is about to happen
between him and
that warrior boy.
It seems during these
100 years, there
were powers I wasn't aware of.
-Energy!
Full blast!
Pierce through!
-Good morning.
And who are you?
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): The Sunlight
Heart didn't pierce him.
Not even a single inch.
-A Buso Renkin?
An Alchemist Warrior, hm?
How fragile.
You lack training.
-Kazuki!
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Pale blue glowing hair.
Olive skin that radiates heat.
A muscular giant,
nearly seven feet tall.
He is--
-The third type of
being that exceeds
both humans and Homunculi.
Oh?
MASTER BUTTERFLY: Good morning.
Good morning, Victor.
-Goodnight, Butterfly.
Death awaits all those
who practice alchemy.
[coughing]
-So this is an energy drain.
-Even though we
destroyed his flask,
he still continues
to get stronger.
If this goes on, none
of us will make it.
KAZUKI: Stop this!
-Impossible.
This is like breathing for me.
It is not my power,
but my biology.
I can't stop it
even if I wanted to.
-Then how can it be stopped?
-If you want to stop it,
then you must kill me.
Do you think you can do that?
So you'll fight me?
Very well.
Of course I never would
have let an Alchemist
Warrior live anyway.
-I'll kill every
single one of you.
-He hates us all.
-If I don't fight,
everyone will die!
Energy, full blast.
Full blast.
Full blast!
Here I come.
Sunlight Crasher!
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Kazuki.
TOKIKO: Kazuki!
Victor!
Kazuki?
-Let's go.
-Yes.
Victor!
-Unless we defeat him
now, everyone will die!
-Useless.
-Tokiko.
Victor!
-I said it was useless.
-Kazuki.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Is power
building up inside him, again?
-Who are you?
Whoever you are, it
seems I better not
fight you empty handed.
Then I too shall
use my Buso Renkin!
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
What is that?
I've never even heard anything
about a black Kakugane.
[groan]
-Fatal Attraction.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
What the-- what is that?
-Kazuki, don't!
This guy's an
unknown entity to us.
We should just stall him until
the Warrior Chief arrives.
-No way.
No one here, even you,
will last that long.
I know I can at least
injure him somehow.
Maybe I can wear him
down little by little!
-Here is your new life.
-He died in vain.
[shout]
-Hmph.
[groan]
-Damn you.
-The closer you get to
me, the faster your energy
will be drained.
What a disgrace.
The Warriors a century ago
were much more composed.
All those who choose
the Warrior path
should be prepared for their
inevitable death in battle.
-You're wrong!
Kazuki's different.
Kazuki was just an
ordinary high school.
And on that spring night
two months ago, I-- I
dragged him into battle.
And I got him--
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): Tokiko?
Is that you crying?
I have to-- keep fighting.
-You think you're the
reason he got killed?
If that's how you feel,
I'll send you to join him.
Living alone and dying
alone is a tragic thing.
[thumping]
-What was that?
-Huh?
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Kazuki's
Kakugane is pulsating.
-Kazuki.
KAZUKI: I will fight.
-Huh?
-I will fight.
-Kazuki.
I will fight.
PAPILLON: Damn it.
What's happening up there?
Mm?
Butterfly's Kakugane.
Just perfect.
I'll use this one
to heal myself.
-I will fight.
I will fight.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Kazuki?
-I will fight.
I will fight.
Fight me!
-Kazuki!
-The only one to die
alone, Victor, is you.
-I see.
You're the same as as me.
So you also traded your
life for the black Kakugane.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): That
spring night two months ago.
What did I do to you, Kazuki?
What have I done?
[theme music]
TOKIKO: I will make it up
to you in any way I can,
for turning you into this.
So please, Kazuki, don't
let your heart change.
Next time, An
Intermediate Existence.
I'll splatter your guts!
-Hi, everyone!
This is Mahiro Muto.
I'm back to properly introduce
you to another Buso Renkin.
For our fifth presentation, we
have the Near Death Happiness.
Yes, that's right.
The Buso Renkin of
that Butterfly weirdo.
Oh sorry, no no, I
mean Mr. Papillon.
Or better yet, Pappy.
I like that better.
Anyway, his name as a
human was Koushaku Chouno,
but now that he's become
a humanoid Homunculi,
the only one who can call him
by that name is my big brother.
Is that the relationship of
enemies, rivals, or friends?
I don't really get
it, but it seems
they have a very deep bond.
Hm.
Oh, well.
Pappy was very sickly back
when he was a human being,
but after doing continuous
research on the Homunculi,
he succeeded in becoming a
humanoid Homunculus himself.
He even obtained a Kakugane,
and now can use a Buso Renkin.
It's called Near
Death Happiness,
which is a Buso Renkin
of black powder.
See those butterfly wings
with black specks growing out
of Pappy's back?
They're actually
made of gunpowder.
The tips of the wings
burn continuously,
allowing him to fly.
How cool is that?
I wanna fly, too!
On top of that, the Near Death
Happiness' special property
allows Pappy to fire the black
powder in any shape he wants.
And he can also
ignite it at will.
That black powder can reach
up to a radius of 164 feet.
But apparently he
can't set it off
unless it's within his eyesight.
Very interesting.
Oh, and by the way, despite
being able to take any shape,
the reason why Pappy
uses the butterfly shape
is because it's just his taste.
Isn't he such a lovely weirdo?
Okie dokie, tune in next time.