[music playing]
NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering essence of
alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name-- Buso Renkin.
[MUSIC - YOSHIKI FUKUYAMA,
"MAKKA NA CHIKAI"]
[clang]
-Hey, wait!
-Hmm?
Hi, Kazuki.
-I need to borrow your uniform.
-(IN UNISON) Hmm?
-Hmm.
OK!
-(IN UNISON) What?
-And then her friends just ran
off and dragged Mahiro away
with them.
-Of course they did.
It doesn't have to
be a girl's uniform.
I just need to be
able to get around
the school without
looking suspicious,
so your gym clothes
would be fine.
-That's right, our gym
uniforms are unisex.
-I'm coming up with a plan
for the search tomorrow.
-Hmm.
One week until the homunculus
embryo reaches her brain.
Only a week.
[dog howling]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Just
one week to settle all this.
-Mm.
[chuckling]
[music playing]
TOKIKO: The physical
characteristics of the Papillon
Masked Creator
are on this paper.
From the lines on the armband,
we know that he's a senior.
There are six senior
year homeroom classes.
If we check two classes per
day, we'll finish in three days,
so it's just a matter of time.
Let me know if you see
someone who fits that profile
and I'll come to confirm.
KAZUKI: We still don't know
what his face looks like.
TOKIKO: You'll know by
the look of his eyes.
It's the color of
rotten river sewage.
[coughing]
-Master, are you all right?
-Hm, I guess it wasn't such a
good idea to ride on your back
without taking my health
into consideration.
-Master, it would be best
if we vacate this place.
-Because of the
Alchemist Warriors?
-Yes.
I believe it's better
to be safe than sorry.
PAPILLON: No, just the opposite.
We should refrain from
any suspicious activity.
If we just let things
take their course,
the female warrior will turn
into a homunculus in a week.
As for the boy, there's no
need to rush into anything.
We just need to be discreet,
keep our eyes open.
Understood?
Kawazui--
-Yes?
-Speaking of the boy, you
still haven't identified him,
correct?
Even though you got a
good look at him up close?
-Sorry, master.
You see, my little ones
can't see very well.
-Hm.
-Well, we just can't
seem to find him.
-Well, of course.
It's only been half a day
since we started searching.
[yawn]
-I guess you're right.
-What, didn't you
get enough sleep?
You need to make sure
you rest at night.
-And what about you?
-Hm?
-Are you OK?
I noticed you've been holding
your stomach since last night.
-Oh, you mean this?
I guess I didn't realize
that I was holding it.
It does feel a bit heavy.
-I see.
[chimes]
-Just don't worry about me.
You should go.
It's the first bell.
-Right.
Next class is-- oh!
Oh no, I'm gonna need
some gym clothes.
-Hm?
-Hey, Mahiro!
Mahiro!
-Huh?
-I need to borrow
your gym clothes.
-OK!
[boing]
-Ohh.
-Where did that come from?
Ohh.
-Where are you, Creator?
[music playing]
[ping]
KAZUKI: Buso Renkin!
[clang]
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
Tokiko told me
to make sure to get
some sleep, but now we
have less than a week.
There is no time for rest.
I need to master the lance
and get the Papillon Masked
Creator.
-Just like yesterday, I'll
start with 1,000 thrusts.
One, two, three, four, five--
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
Where are you, Creator?
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Where are you?
[music playing]
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): Where?
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Where is he?
[music playing]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
He's not here.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
He's nowhere to be found!
[grunting]
-Damn it!
PAPILLON: Really?
So they're looking all over
the school for me, huh?
They must be having a hard time.
-But master, regarding
the male warrior.
-Hmm, you still
can't identify him?
It seems the little ones have
bad eyesight, isn't that right?
It's just as well.
We've got the upper
hand right now anyway.
As soon as I recover,
I'll conclude
all of my research
done up until now
and begin the final experiment.
-Oh, so hungry.
I haven't been able to
eat anything lately.
I think I've reached my limit.
[chimes]
KAZUKI: The Papillon Masked
Creator can't be found
and I'm getting nowhere
with my training.
And to top it off, my lack
of sleep and sore muscles
from the training are
beginning to catch up with me.
[moan]
-Don't sound so pathetic.
-I can't help it.
-Let's just wrap up
the search for now.
It appears as though
we're completely off
the mark in how and
where we're searching.
We'll just need to rethink
things and start over tomorrow.
I think it's for the
best, you got it?
-OK.
Understood.
-You've gotta shake it off.
[sigh]
-But what about--
-It'll be OK.
We still have time.
Besides, it's not like we've
completely wasted our time up
until now.
Since we started our
search four days ago,
he's obviously taken action and
raised his guard against us.
In other words, during
these past four days,
there haven't been any victims.
This is obviously a direct
result of what we're doing.
For now, let's just think about
what we'll do after tomorrow.
You should go home and
get a good night's sleep.
You look exhausted.
-Right.
Then I'll see you tomorrow.
Tomorrow we're gonna get the
Creator for sure, Tokiko!
[chuckling]
[grunt]
[groan]
-Tokiko is so
incredible and fierce.
She truly is one
hell of a warrior.
I need to try
harder and catch up.
I know, I should
just ask her what
I need to do to master
the Buso Renkin.
Tokiko!
[gasp]
[panting]
TOKIKO: It'll be OK.
There's still time.
[music playing]
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
I've gotta try harder.
[gasp]
[groan]
[heartbeat]
[chuckling]
-That girl sure looks tasty.
[slurping]
[growl]
-Aiee!
I want to eat her so badly
I can hardly stand it.
The Creator may be interested in
creating an Alchemist Warrior,
but I don't know.
That really isn't
any of my concern.
Besides, I wouldn't
be able to eat her
if she became a homunculus.
Three days left until
the expiration date.
I've got to eat her up quick.
But I guess it'll have to
be you first, Kazuki Muto.
You did kill my little ones
the other night, didn't you?
Well, now you're
going to have to pay
for that, my friend--
with your life!
-Bring it on.
-Aiee.
Aren't you a brave little one?
-I won't let you
lay a finger on her.
I'll defeat you and make
you talk about the Creator.
-How delusional.
You can't beat me.
Just look at you.
You're a pathetic human.
-You don't scare me.
I may be inexperienced,
but I will not
let Tokiko fight tonight.
Besides her, I'm the
only one in this town who
can fight any of you
and I'm not afraid.
-How arrogant.
Well, you both will die anyway.
[chuckling]
TOKIKO: Kazuki,
didn't are you there?
I'm coming in.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
He's not here, huh?
Oh well, I'll just leave the
gym clothes he let me borrow.
Hm, so this workout is the
reason for his lack of sleep.
Hmm, that's so cute.
But he will never master the
Buso Renkin doing it this way.
-Kazuki, look what I got!
Real beauties,
totally your type.
Just like that-- gah,
ya, hee, Tokiko--
-Hmm?
I see.
So Kazuki likes this
kind of stuff, huh?
But I guess this
is yours, though.
You really should
control your perversions.
-Ohh!
I am not a pervert!
-Hey, Tokiko, what
are you doing here.
-Well, I just came to
return something I borrowed.
-Oh.
Then I'll let him know
when he gets back.
-Huh?
He hasn't come back yet?
-I don't think so.
-He didn't show up
for dinner, either.
[worried noise]
-Tokiko?
-Wait!
Stop!
-We're on the second floor!
-(IN UNISON) Tokiko!
-Where'd she go?
-She's gone.
-Hm.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
That kid's doing
something reckless
by himself again.
[music playing]
KAZUKI: Buso Renkin!
-Your own personal war cry?
Well, here's mine.
-Homunculus transform.
Well, what do you know?
A riverbed in the dark
of night on the outskirts
of town and not one
single soul around.
The perfect place for
savoring a fresh meal.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): This is the
first time I've had a face off
like this, one on one with
a homunculus all by myself.
-What's wrong?
Why are your legs shaking, boy?
[grunt]
-I'm completely aware
of my inexperience,
but I'm also the only
one in this town who'll
be able to fight you!
And that's what I intend to do.
-You don't get it, do you?
Just adding a little bit of
will to fight is not enough.
The void that separates
homunculus from humans
is much bigger than that.
[gasp]
[groaning]
-How sad.
You can't even dodge
direct attacks.
Well, I guess this
is the end for you.
[frogs croaking]
[groan]
-Over so soon?
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
No matter how much
he may have practiced,
mastering the Buso
Renkin is another story.
If he fights now, the only
thing waiting for him is death.
-Aiee!
I got a prize!
Now all I have to do is eat
that girl and I'll get one more.
And maybe once I bring
two pieces of Kakugane
back as offerings to my
master, he will forgive me.
[chuckling]
KAWAZUI: But wait.
How am I supposed to revert
this back to a Kakugane?
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): What?
I'm still alive?
Oh, that's right, my
chest is empty, isn't it?
That means I'm still alive,
even if I've been stabbed.
Ow.
Dying really hurts like hell.
Even though it does
this much, I bet
Tokiko would endure
it and try to hide it.
Mahiro would probably
cry her eyes out.
[grunt]
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): I wonder how
Okakura, Daihama, and Rokumasu
would do.
No way.
I don't want to make anyone
suffer this kind of pain.
-Hmm?
-Don't take what isn't
yours without asking.
[chuckling]
-I see.
Well, I guess you
must enjoy pain
since you're asking
for more, eh?
-I'll endure it no matter
how horrible the pain is.
Tokiko gave me this
new life and this power
that resides in me now is
not just to protect myself.
It's the power to fight and
protect everyone from monsters
like you.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whatever.
Will you just die already?
[grunt]
-My little ones!
You killed them!
-What's this?
[gasp]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Buso
Renkin is one's own fighting
instinct manifested into a form.
Only in a battle, when
your life is on the line,
will you feel and understand
its special properties.
Training will only
begin after that.
You haven't gotten
there yet, Kazuki.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): I get it.
Tokiko's Valkyrie Skirt has four
robotic arms that move quickly
and precisely.
My lance has this
ornamental cloth
that morphs my will
to fight into energy.
This is the special
property of my Buso Renkin.
-I demand you tell me
about the Creator now!
-Not a chance.
Do you know how
much nutrition is
necessary to create
one small frog?
I must eat, and I'm
going to eat her first.
-No way will I let you do that!
-Aah!
-Yaa!
[wail]
[groan]
[groaning]
[grunt]
-Huh?
[wailing]
-OK, OK, I promise I
won't eat her, I do!
I won't eat any other humans.
Don't kill me, please,
I beg you, please!
Oh!
-Do you really mean it?
-Huh?
-You have to promise.
-I do, I do!
Really, I promise!
I promise!
-Then I'll ask one
more time-- where
is the Papillon Masked Creator?
Where the hell is he?
-Oh, a piece of cake.
You guys are just too dumb.
The school isn't the only
building on the campus
that students use.
Ah!
[wailing]
-I won't be
patronizing, I promise!
Just spare me!
[sobbing]
-Uh-- huh?
What?
My, my, my, my.
How dare you try
intimidating me.
Take this!
And this!
What was he thinking?
I'm finally saved.
HANABUSA: No, now
you're finally through.
[screaming]
-My master is well aware of
your scheming and conniving
behavior.
[scream]
-Disgusting frog.
All those who dare defy
my master disgust me.
[phone ringing]
TOKIKO: Don't move any further.
If you do, I'll kill you.
-What if I don't move?
-Then I'll make
it a quick death.
[chuckling]
-I'm actually impressed
you found this place.
-I've already checked out
all of your feeding grounds.
Buso Ren--
[groaning]
-You poor fragile little thing.
No matter how hard you resist,
it's just a matter of time
before you become one of us.
[chuckling]
[grunt]
-Buso Renkin!
[music playing]
[grunt]
-If I am to become a monster,
I'm planning to kill as many
of you as possible before then.
Even if I become one,
the first thing I'll do
is destroy the Papillon
Masked Creator.
You monsters shouldn't
underestimate an Alchemist
Warrior.
-Disgusting.
Those words, that
attitude, that tone.
Those who interfere with the
creator cannot be forgiven!
-Shut up, man-eater!
[music playing]
-This is the power my
master has given me.
These 100 thorns won't let
even a single bug through.
-I warned you before.
I would have given you
a more pleasant death
if you hadn't moved.
[groaning]
-Now go to hell!
I'll splatter your guts!
[screaming]
[explosion]
[groan]
TOKIKO: It uses your
survival instinct
to raise the level of
your healing powers.
Another one of the
Kakugane's abilities.
-Tokiko, why are you here?
I told you to follow my
instructions, didn't I?
Why did you fight alone?
-Arrogance.
I'm so sorry.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
I'm such a bad liar.
-Anyway, this is what
will happen to you
if you do things your own way.
[grunt]
[groan]
-Hey, lie back down
and stay still.
Your wounds are
still pretty fresh.
-Listen, Tokiko, I figured out
that that ornamental cloth that
morphs into energy is the
special property of my lance,
and that's how I managed
to defeat a homunculus.
TOKIKO: You defeated
a homunculus?
KAZUKI: Yeah, that
disgusting frog-man.
But look where it got me.
-Uh-- it's all right.
You're still inexperienced
-Yeah, I know.
I have to try much, much harder.
-That's right.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): But you've
become a little stronger today.
Have a good rest for now so
you can do your best again
tomorrow.
[MUSIC - YOSHIAKI DEWA,
"HOSHIAKARI"]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Up till
now, the Creator's homunculi
were all prototypes.
His final product is the
one he is still building.
Next time on Buso Renkin,
"Another New Life."
I'll splatter your guts!