NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
NESCASTOR: Three days
ago, the residents
of an old family estate
vanished mysteriously.
Officials have no
leads for what seems
to be a modern case of
being spirited away.
In addition, the number of
missing person cases here
in Ginsei City has been
increasing steadily
since the beginning
of the-- year!
Hey!
Watch it!
Who are you people?
-Hey, Kazuki!
Are you watchin'?
-There are still traces
of your blood here.
10 days ago, you
unwillingly became
involved in the world
of alchemy and combat.
I still can't help but
feel responsible for that.
But you've really
done a good job.
KAZUKI: I haven't
done any good at all.
In the end, I wasn't
able to carry out
any of the things I
vowed that I would do.
And what's more, I killed
Chouno with my own hands.
And in the end, he said to me--
-Don't apologize, you hypocrite!
-I did the best I could.
But I-- maybe I am a
hypocrite after all.
-Kazuki--
-For good or for evil,
there is no shame
in holding to your beliefs
until the very end.
If you don't know whether
or not you're a hypocrite,
then continue
fighting, Kazuki Muto.
-Warrior Chief?
-He's the Warrior Chief?
-The next battle
will soon begin.
-The next battle?
-Will you continue to fight?
If you're willing, then by
the authority vested in me,
I proclaim you an
Alchemist Warrior.
-Your English
teacher, Mr. Mida, has
been in the hospital
due to illness.
Therefore, starting this week--
-If you don't know whether
or not you're a hypocrite,
then continue
fighting, Kazuki Muto.
TEACHER: Now I will introduce
a new transfer student.
Please come in.
[interested chatter]
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER): Tokiko.
-This is Tokiko
Tsumura, and as of today
she'll be your new classmate.
BOY: What an awful scar.
It's kind of scary.
BOY: What do you
think happened to her?
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
It's the same story
as the last school
I infiltrated.
I'm better off being a loner
than in a place like this.
-So, would you like
to introduce yourself?
-I've got nothing to say.
-Huh?
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): Yes,
it's better this way.
I wouldn't be able to enjoy
a school life now, anyway.
-Um, OK.
So then, does anyone have
any questions for Tokiko?
-Yeah!
-What the hell is your
relationship with Kazuki?
Are you guys going out?
We're all dying to know!
-Yeah!
I have a right to know, too!
-Mavy, this isn't our class!
-Come on, our class
already started.
GIRL: So you're friends with
the four stooges plus one?
I mean, what kind of
relationship do you guys have?
-Yeah, now we all want to know.
[crowd talking over each other]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
On second though, this
is a little different
from the last school.
-No questions about my scar
or relationship to Kazuki.
Anyone else?
-When's your birthday?
What's your sign?
-August 7th, which
makes me a Leo.
-So where do you live?
-The dorms, starting today.
-Why aren't you
wear our uniform?
-It flaps around, and it's
hard to move around in it.
-Any hobbies or talents?
-Training and changing
clothes quickly.
-So what's your type?
-I'm not interested in love.
-Tell them to make me squeal.
-You stupid pig.
Wait a minute!
Who was that?
The last one wasn't a question.
Who was it?
-They're having so much fun.
-So just tell us, what
is your relationship?
-Let's just say I'm willing
to keep that secret.
-I'm alive.
-Ah.
You're awake.
Goodmorning, Koushaku.
Or are you now Papillon?
-Who are you?
-I never thought one
of my descendants
would decipher the clues I
left in my research notes
and manage to recreate my
work after a hundred years.
I guess it pays to be immortal.
-Complete the research?
Immortal?
My great great grandfather,
Bakushaku Chouno?
-I discarded that name after
I was no longer a human.
My brethren in battle now
refer to me as Dr. Butterfly.
Welcome, Papillon.
In acknowledgement of your
superior intellect and ability
to take action, I
welcome you to the League
of Extraordinary Elect, the LXE.
First of all, you will need
to restore that body of yours,
and then you shall be
granted the true power
of the humanoid
Homunculus that you still
haven't been able to
successfully achieve.
That way you won't be defeated
by mere humans ever again.
-So tell me, how do you feel?
-Magnificent.
KAZUKI: So you think
you're fitting in?
TOKIKO: Yes.
Thanks to you.
KAZUKI: But you're
older than I am,
so why are you in
the same class as me?
-Maybe the Warrior Chief
did it for the mission,
to make it easier to execute.
But to be honest, it
was actually easier
to function the way
things were before.
I was able to move
around more freely.
-So what's the
Warrior Chief like?
-He's the way you just saw him.
He's very mysterious, and always
hide himself in that coat.
I don't know much about him, not
even his name, or background,
or anything, for that matter.
-A man of mystery, huh?
Maybe it's just because
it's cooler that way.
-Don't be silly.
That's probably not the reason.
-All I know without a doubt
is that whenever he shows up,
a big battle's about to happen.
The other thing I
can tell you for sure
is that he has a habit of
always saying the word bravo.
BRAVO: All right.
So as of today, I'm going to be
the new manager of this dorm.
And you can just call
me Captain Bravo!
-Warrior Chief?
-Um, excuse me?
Why don't you just tell
us what your real name is?
-Bravo.
Looks like you're
a smart young lady.
However, my real
name's a secret.
And that's because
it's cooler that way.
-Tokiko, that manager--
-That's right.
I really don't want
to believe it, but--
-The two of us are going
to get along great.
-Are you really that stupid?
-Huh?
-Haven't you figured it out?
-What?
-Well, well, well.
The fool and the
straight man there
with the makeout
strawberry stuff
while someone's taking the
time to introduce themselves.
Report to my office.
I'd like a word with
the both of you.
PAPILLON: A story?
DR. BUTTERFLY: Yes.
A story from over 100 years
ago, when I was still human.
Back then, everyone was
already skeptical of alchemy,
and many dismissed it.
But I knew there
was more to it, so I
began to completely
immerse myself in research.
Yet, there was only so
much I could do on my own.
I did identify the existence
of Homunculi and Kakugane,
but ended up running
out of leads.
And then he appeared.
-Who?
KAZUKI: A traitor?
-That's right.
100 years ago there
was a man who,
despite being an
alchemist warrior,
turned himself into a
Homunculus and fled.
-Yes, I've heard that before.
As I recall, he was
a strong warrior
who was chased all
the way to Japan,
and was cornered
by his pursuers.
Eventually, at the very end
he got away, disappeared,
and has been missing
ever since then.
-Bravo.
Great memory, Warriors Tokiko.
Now, over a century later,
because of the recent incident
involving Papillon, we now
know about an alchemist
named Bakushaku Chouno.
And we've determined that
he and the Warrior Traitor
have joined forces here.
-When I first met him,
he was seriously injured.
So in exchange for his
knowledge of alchemy,
I pledged to heal him
once I had finished
conducting my research.
It took 100 years,
but it appears
I have finally succeeded.
-I see.
So I'm nothing more
than the guinea pig.
-Remember, he is the
leader of the LXE,
and he is the one
who will become
the king of all
Homunculi one day.
-Really?
Then I guess I should vacate
this throne to make room.
Right?
-Can this be?
The restoration flask's power?
Or is it--
-I have one favor to ask.
I wonder if you'd prepare
some fabulous clothes for me.
There's someone I can't
wait to meet again.
-The mission this
time around is to get
to the bottom of the League
of Extraordinary Elects led
by Dr. Butterfly,
and destroy it.
-Well, the fact that a
name has been confirmed,
it seems the investigation is
already being conducted, sir.
-Yes.
I have already
deployed a warrior
that I brought with
me three days ago.
-So including you and
that warrior, three of us
are assigned to the mission?
-No.
We might have to go it alone.
His report stopped
coming two days ago.
Which is why I need to ask you.
Kazuki Muto, will
you join our fight?
It appears that you're
still undecided.
-I don't know.
I'm still torn about
the whole thing.
You see, half of
me wants to keep
fighting those bad guys that
are still out there using
the power of our alchemy.
But the other half of me is
afraid that I'll mess up again,
like I did with Chouno.
[phone ringing]
-Honestly, I don't think
you should fight anymore.
You really should just leave
the fighting to us warriors,
and go back to your
normal high school life.
BRAVO: Muto!
-Huh?
-A phone call.
He says that he's
a friend of yours.
-A friend of mine?
I wonder who it is?
Yeah?
Hello?
-Oh, you poor thing.
You sound dispirited.
How strange that I,
the one who lost,
is cheerful, while
you, the one who won,
sound depressed and miserable.
You're worrying me a bit.
How about you and I meet
tomorrow, Kazuki Muto?
-Koushaku Chouno!
[shocked whispers]
-Oh, yoo-hoo.
Over here.
-Koushaku Chouno.
-Why don't we go
inside somewhere,
instead of standing
here talking?
Oh, one hamburger meal A,
and two medium coffees.
Yum.
-Yes, sir.
Will that be for here?
Or maybe you'd like it to go?
-For here.
-Thank you, sir.
Enjoy.
-Just relax.
You don't have to
be so vigilant.
I have no intention
of fighting today.
-Leave the clowning to
your hideous outfit.
-Clowning?
About what?
This outfit of mine
is magnificent.
In fact, it is so marvelous
I could wear it to a ball.
Right, Muto?
-Certainly better than
seeing you in your underwear.
-Underwear?
-Oh, come, now.
I was very fond of
that outfit, too.
It was pretty damn cool.
-Your definition
of cool is way off.
Now, the mask is another story.
That is kind of cool.
-Don't encourage him!
Just take off that mask now.
-That I cannot do.
I'll never take it off in
front of people ever again.
It is a testament to me
abandoning my human life.
I had my body
completely restored,
but unfortunately the disease
is still inside of me,
as it was before.
I actually haven't recovered
enough of my physical strength
to fight yet, either.
And apparently I
haven't obtained
the so-called true power.
-True power?
-Muto, you don't seem to
be at your best, either.
So for the time being,
let's just declare war.
We can find when we're
both more prepared.
Something to look forward to.
-In that case, there was no
reason for me to come at all.
-Huh?
-Captain Bravo?
-Warrior Chief?
-Miss, I too shall have
a hamburger meal A!
-Are you going to want
that for here, sir?
Or will that be to go, instead?
-For here.
-Manager!
-This one is on the house, so
please just take it to go, sir.
-What wonderful service.
Bravo!
I think I'll start
coming here all the time!
PAPILLON: Me, too.
This place is magnificent.
[doorbell]
-Mm.
The flavor of blood is
absolutely delicious.
-That's the taste of the
blood you coughed up.
-So that was it, huh?
I guess that's all right.
Hm.
I wonder how many years it's
been since I've been to school?
-Serve the ball!
-Here it comes!
Eat this!
-What, dodgeball?
-But things haven't
really changed at all.
No matter whose
voice I hear, it only
sounds like people mocking me.
Even after having been
reborn as a superhuman,
it seems the world
hasn't changed at all.
As I thought before,
maybe it would be best
to burn it all down, and then
create a magnificent world that
suits me, and is only for me.
-So the LXE doesn't satisfy
you enough, Koushaku Chouno?
-I've had enough seclusion
in the past, you see.
And by the way, don't you ever
dare call me Chouno again.
Only Kazuki Muto may
call me by that name.
Muto, I'm not quite sure
why you're not yourself,
and the truth is I don't care.
Eventually I'll settle things
with you once and for all.
Until I do, I won't be able to
be myself, and truly take off.
KAZUKI: Chouno.
I also plan to settle things
with you once and for all.
-Good.
Your fighting spirit's returned.
That makes me kind of happy.
-Do you know what you're
getting into, Kazuki?
Settling things means
killing him one more time.
Do you really think
you can do that?
Can you kill him again?
-Sorry to interrupt.
However, it appears
something urgent has come up.
Another enemy.
But unlike Papillon, this one
seems to possess true power.
MOONFACE: Moon?
-The experiment is a success.
-So we'll finally
be able to heal him?
-It'll have to be done
after the maintenance,
so we won't be able
to do it right away.
-I just can't wait.
By the way, what about Papillon?
-He couldn't wait to go
out in the elegant suit I
prepared for him.
He went to settle some
unfinished business
with a warrior.
Probably an
associative of the one
we took care of the other day.
MOONFACE: Oh, my.
Will he be all right?
-There won't be any problems.
I sent Kinjo to
keep an eye on him.
-Homunculus!
-Buso--
-Renkin!
Buso Renkin of the Right Hand
Gauntlet, Peaky Gulliver!
-The difference between a
humanoid and an animal type
isn't just what they eat,
or that the humanoid has
superior power while
maintaining its human form.
No matter how much human
knowledge an animal type
acquires, it can only
fight instinctively
with its claws and fangs.
A humanoid can fight with a
command of various weapons,
using their own
fighting instincts.
In other words--
-They're able to use Kakugane as
a Buso Renkin, just like we do.
-So this is the true power
of the humanoid Homunculi?
-I'll deal with you
little weaklings later.
Hey, you in the coat!
I'll start with you first!
Homunculus power which exceeds
humans, and Buso Renkin
power exceeding
all modern science!
Do you really think you can beat
the most powerful combination
of these two elements with
your single Buso Renkin alone?
-We can, and we will.
That is why we Alchemist
Warriors exist.
-Buso Renkin!
Buso Renkin of the
Lance, Sunlight Heart!
Energy full blast!
Go now!
-I said that I would deal with
you little weaklings later!
-Jousting renamed
to Sunlight Slasher!
His fist suddenly got huge.
-Why are you so surprised?
You should know better.
A Buso Renkin is
no ordinary weapon.
This is the special property
of my Peaky Gulliver!
Yahoo!
-You lousy-- All right,
I'll burst through
with the Sunlight Slasher!
-You wish.
Laputa Falls!
No way will a
Homunculus ever lose
to a mere human
in a power match.
-Kazuki!
Are you all right, Kazuki?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
But this guy is tough.
-I know that.
Buso--
-You two stay back.
I'll deal with him.
-Warrior Chief.
-This guy's a small fry,
but he's more than you
two can handle right now.
-Me?
A small fry?
What a lousy judge of enemies.
-As I recall, that Kakugane
had the serial number 52.
-You got good eyes.
It's been three days, but I
got the all clear from Moonface
to use this weapon he got
from the Warrior he defeated.
By any chance, was he
one of your subordinates?
I'm sensing something here.
Are you suddenly blind with
anger, Mr. Alchemist Warrior?
-No.
A Warrior's defeat means death.
I'm not angry about that.
-Wow, that's pretty darn cold.
Well, here goes.
Brobdingnag Knuckles!
What's this?
It's like steel.
This is not possible.
No way.
-Buso Renkin of
the Metal Jacket.
Silver Skin.
The service both turns into
hard metal and regenerates
instantly when
something strikes it.
You think I wear this outfit
because I like how it looks?
-Uh.
-Not bad at all.
But it's just a
defense Buso Renkin.
Not a real weapon.
So, Finger Strike!
-But I do have a weapon.
My Warrior body is my weapon.
-You-- You are angry
after all, aren't you?
-I told you already.
I'm not angry at all.
-Wow.
So strong.
What?
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
Bravo really isn't angry.
He looked like he was
about to cry at any moment.
-Bravo.
Tokiko.
OK, I'll do it.
If we allow the LXE
to continue to exist,
this town will go to pieces.
Somebody's gotta fight them
now, so that Mahiro, my friends,
and all the people in school
and in town can live in peace.
Being called a hypocrite.
Feeling the pain
of my own shame.
I think I can live with it.
I think I can bear
it if I want to help
free people from
suffering and sadness.
I've decided.
I'll keep fighting as
long as we need to.
Captain Bravo.
Please make me into
an Alchemist Warrior.
-Kazuki Muto.
You can't always rely on
your Buso Renkin alone.
If you keep on fighting the way
you have been all this time,
you'll never win, and
you'll get yourself killed.
In order to make you into
an Alchemist Warrior,
I'll train you without mercy.
If you don't want to
perish, sink your teeth
in with a do or die resolve.
Got it?
-Hm.
[theme music]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Another enemy
has shown up targeting
the perfect place to feed.
The school dorm.
Never again will I let
that tragedy repeat itself.
I'll kill that
Homunculus for sure!
Next time, A Night in the Dorm.
I'll splatter your guts!