NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form,
creating a weapon like other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[music playing]
NARRATOR: The decisive
battle with the League
of Extraordinary Elects or
L.X.E. has come to an end.
However, Victor has
been resurrected.
In the course of this
battle with Victor,
Kazuki himself has transformed
into a form similar
to Victor's.
With Victor's flight,
the mission is completed.
Kazuki and the others
have gone to the beach
for a brief vacation.
But--
-You don't want to involve
the others, now, do you?
Why don't we take our time
to talk it over tonight?
-There's no place
like the beach.
[laughs]
-An octopus!
-Whoa.
-Yeah!
-Yeah.
-Yah!
I I told you to quit
staring at my naval.
-Bravo!
Yeah, bravo!
-Hey Rokumasu, where
did Okakura go?
-Well, I'm not quite sure,
but I think I might know.
-Hey, ladies.
Want to get a drink?
[giggling]
-What a funny face.
-Hey.
Hey there.
-I hate the beach
with a passion.
-Hey, what's with Okakura?
-Well, I'm not quite sure,
but I think I might know.
-Bravo?
-Bravo.
Don't be discouraged.
Some things are more
rewarding in the end
when you keep on trying.
Maybe I should just demonstrate
to make things easier.
Hello, ladies.
Watch closely now.
Here goes.
Bravo Arts 1 of 13!
-Warrior chief.
-The enchanting Bravo Kiss.
-What was--
-For a moment there
I felt kind of funny.
-What do you think?
-Master, please, take
me under your wing.
-Enchanting Kazuki Kiss.
-You ever do that again and
I'll splatter your guts.
-Got it.
-By the way, I'm
the only one who
can use this technique, because
it's one of a kind Bravo art.
-That's not fair.
-All right, let's go
to clean up for dinner,
and then we'll shoot some
fireworks around nine.
-Roger.
-Got it.
-So about your belly
button, Tokiko.
-What is it with the two
of you and belly buttons?
-So tell me,
Kazuki, did anything
happen while I was gone?
-Well, Let's see.
Nobody from the L.X.E.
Came looking for us.
Chono hasn't shown himself
even once since then.
So nothing happened, I guess.
We've had nothing but peace.
-That's very good to hear.
-By the way, Bravo,
once things settle down,
will you continue
training me like before?
I'm no match for
Victor like this.
And if I'd been
stronger then, maybe I
would have been able to
prevent Victor's restoration.
I'm still not strong enough.
I want to become a stronger
alchemist warrior, Bravo.
-200.
Oh, my back is killing me.
-Hey, Kazuki, let's
do rock paper scissors
to see who carries
the bags next.
-Coming.
-Kazuki.
Tonight after midnight meet me
over at the rocks to the west.
-Let's eat!
-Everything looks so good.
Touch my food, you die.
All right, then I'm
going to take yours.
-Over my dead body.
-Hey, knock it off, Rokumasu.
My food!
-What's wrong, Tokiko?
-Huh?
Oh, nothing.
-You haven't touched
your food at all.
Did you lose your
appetite or something?
-Oh, no.
It's not that at all.
-Well in that case, get ready to
eat plenty of food, all right?
-Well, uh, I guess so.
[laughter]
-Hey, wait!
[snoring]
-Hey, Bravo.
Wait a sec.
Bravo, where's Tokiko?
-Sorry to keep you
waiting, Gota Nakamura.
-You remembered me, huh?
That's so nice of you.
-Buso Renkin.
Tell me.
Why are you here?
-Already bearing your fangs?
You really are quite
the warrior, aren't you?
I've got to say, that happens
to be one of your best traits,
Tokiko.
Thanks for your support
with my training back then.
As of now, I'm officially
an alchemist warrior, just
like you, Tokiko.
-Skip the pleasantries.
Hurry and explain
why you are here.
-Hey, that's pretty cold.
But that too is one of the
great things about you.
-So what did you
call me out here for?
-I'm here to deliver your new
assignment from headquarters.
It's the same mission that
I've been assigned to.
-I wonder if she got lost.
-Kazuki, how much of you
heard from Warrior Tokiko
about the main
purpose of our forces?
-How much?
Well, let's see.
Just that it
safeguards the kakugane
and defeats the
Homunculi, but you know,
actually I haven't
been told its name yet.
-I see.
Well then, I'll
start from there.
The organization that
binds us alchemist warriors
together is called
the Alchemist Army.
-The Alchemist Army?
-It all started with
the alchemist guilds
of medieval England.
Over the years it has grown
into a secret society governing
every aspect of alchemy.
It has three main purposes.
Two of them you already
know, but there is one more.
The creation of the
philosopher's stone.
Even those who are not
really familiar with alchemy
have heard of it before.
It is the transmutation
of base metals
into precious metals, the quest
for attaining immortality.
This all powerful stone
represents that crystallization
of all alchemy, making
all miracles possible.
After many long
years of research,
the Alchemist Army had a
breakthrough 100 years ago.
They used the kakugane with
serial numbers one, two,
and three to create
three prototypes.
And those became--
-The black kakugane.
-Correct.
And the first person to be
chosen as a test subject
was great warrior Victor.
In a fierce battle
with the Homunculi,
Victor's heart was
severely damaged.
In order to save his
life, he Alchemist Army
replaced it right away with
the prototype black kakugane
serial number one.
The result, as you
know, was that Victor
changed into a monster even
greater than the Homunculi.
And for the time,
the Alchemist Army
was driven to the
brink of destruction.
Amidst the chaos,
several kakugane,
including the remaining
two black kakugane,
found their way into
the outside world.
Since then, all research
on the philosopher's stone
has been indefinitely suspended.
-What about the story of
Victor turning himself
into a Homunculus and
becoming a traitor?
-Well, that was a cover up
story to hide the organization's
greatest failure.
The reason warrior
Tokiko implanted
the kakugane in your chest was
because the story she heard
about Victor's
transplant was incorrect.
It has taken me an entire
month to really dig and uncover
this information about Victor
and the black kakugane.
And it took me another
month to investigate
both you and your
condition, Kazuki.
When you were at
our hospital, you
underwent an extensive
physical exam.
After carefully
analyzing those results
and studying records of what
transpired with your Victor
form, all findings
confirm that your body
and the black kakugane
have become linked
and can no longer be
separated from one another.
In other words, you will never
be able to be human again.
OK what are you
talking about, Bravo?
I mean, really, look at me.
I think I look pretty
human right now.
-One doesn't become
like Victor all at once.
There are stages.
And you are still at stage one.
If my calculations are
correct, your transformation
will be complete
in about six weeks.
By the end of the
summer, you will
be just like Victor, a monster
whose mere existence brings
death and destruction
to all around it.
Before that happens you
must be disposed of.
That is my new mission.
-Bravo.
-You were killed
by a Homunculus.
The life that Warrior
Tokiko gave you
should never have
been given to anyone.
You must be killed once
again to set things right.
-Bravo!
-Kazuki Muto must
be re-exterminated.
-What did you just say?
Explain what you
just said to me.
Are you telling me you're
here to kill Kazuki?
-No.
Of course not.
They don't give this
kind of job to rookies.
I'm just supposed to keep you
here until the job is done.
However, I could
take this guy Kazuki
if I were given a fair chance.
-If not you then who?
Who could it be?
Someone at this beach?
Some other warrior?
It can't be.
Where are they now?
-I cannot tell you.
A warrior's mission
is a sacred duty.
-You're right.
I'll search myself.
-Five kilometers east of here.
Deep into the craggy area.
-Thank you, Gota.
I owe you one.
I'm happy you achieved your
wish of becoming a warrior.
Congratulations.
-When she's not acting tough,
she's not so bad either.
Oh no, what did I just do?
You mustn't, Tokiko.
It's too dangerous to go now.
Captain Bravo means business.
-Say it isn't so, Bravo.
Please tell me you're
kidding, Bravo.
Just say it.
It's a lie!
Lie, lie, lie, lie!
You are lying!
-For good or for evil,
there is no shame
in holding to your beliefs
until the very end.
-The same words he used when
he recruited me as a warrior.
-My mission is to save
as many people as I can.
And to do that, I'm even willing
to kill a fellow warrior if I
need to.
I would even become evil itself.
-So it's true.
The man standing before me
really is Captain Bravo.
-Now, will you lay down
your life willingly?
Kazuki.
-I understand.
But not now.
I won't give up just yet.
I can't.
Don't you see that those
are the same words that
encouraged me to become
an alchemist warrior,
believing in my own
convictions like you?
If six weeks is all I have
left as a human being,
then I'm going to pursue my
convictions to the very end.
And I will fight until then
with the life Tokiko's given me.
I will.
-Kazuki, you really
have grown strong.
-That's why I intend to fight.
Buso Renkin!
Something's wrong with
the sunlight heart.
Could it be there's
still some damage
left from the
battle with Victor?
What's this?
-Just like Victor's battle
records from a century ago.
You yourself have
already changed,
so your Buso Renkin
is changing with you.
Kazuki will get even stronger.
That is why I must
finish him off
before he becomes
even more powerful.
-What is this?
The sunlight heart
is changing form.
Wait, is this?
Could this possibly
be my new lance?
-Yes.
That is your new strength.
Take it in your hand.
Show me its power.
-It's smaller and
lighter than before
and I can wield it
easily with one hand.
Now I can execute everything
I've learned thus far.
But.
-Its reach has become
that much shorter,
and its destructive power
has also been reduced.
He's missing his mark even
when he aims correctly.
The lance will fail as a
weapon if it lacks the power
to kill with a single blow.
-Come on.
Reach him.
Reach him, please!
-What?
Slash bravo chop.
-It's already begun.
-Wait for me, Tokiko.
Wait, Tokiko!
-I see.
This new lance is the
eternal energy type.
It has the special feature
of activating and expanding
as needed.
It is a good lance.
Its size and power
can be adjusted
to suit the needs of a battle.
However, with your
new Buso Renkin
alone, you can't possibly
beat by silver skin or me.
-I already knew that he was
strong, but he's really strong.
-Come at me with
everything you've got.
The warrior chief
commands a domain
far superior to anything
you have ever imagined.
If you want to see the smiles
of your friends, your sister
and Warrior Tokiko
once again, then you'd
better fight me with
everything you've got.
-All right.
Here I come, Bravo.
I'll repel the silver
skin to end this battle.
-So this is the power
of the black kakugane.
But ultimately the man
who must be defeated
has powers far
greater than this.
If I cannot prevail
against Kazuki now,
how will I ever defeat Victor?
-I've crushed it!
I'll use this to--
-You'll use this to do what?
Silver Skin, another type.
I have taken your
most powerful attack
and I too shall give you in
return everything I've got.
Here I come.
-What?
-Silver Skin, reverse.
-Silver Skin reverse?
What the?
Again.
I can't move my fist.
-Not just your fist.
You'll find that your
entire body is paralyzed.
That is the power of
Silver Skin reverse.
The regular Silver Skin
is a powerful metal jacket
that completely blocks out
attacks from the outside.
But if it is reversed,
its characteristics
are inverted, preventing an
enemy from releasing an attack.
It becomes an
invisible straitjacket
averting all offensive
action by the attacker.
Of course, it does not only
shut out physical attacks.
It seems to recognize your
energy drain as an attack
as well.
This battle is over.
Surrender, Kazuki.
It's not too late.
If you do so now, you can
still die as a human being.
-No.
Not yet.
Those smiles.
I'm not ready to give them up.
-Another type of reverse, also
known as the double straight.
Farewell to do, Kazuki Muto.
-Bravo.
No.
[inaudible]
Okakura.
Everyone.
Tokiko.
-Kazuki!
-Warrior Tokiko, halt.
That's an order.
-I cannot listen to that order.
-Don't forget that
you're a warrior.
Go and cool your head.
-Tokiko!
-Warrior Gota.
-Forgive me.
[phone ringing]
-Has Kazuki Muto been properly
re-exterminated, Sakimori?
-Hewatari.
-Tokiko.
Are you all right?
-Kazuki!
Let go.
If I don't help
him soon he will--
-What are you saying?
Just calm down.
It's hopeless.
He's already dead.
Besides, with your
legs in that shape,
it's not possible for
you to swim on your own.
-I don't care.
Let go.
Where are you, Kazuki?
Kazuki!
-Give up on him, Tokiko.
There's no way Captain Bravo
would leave unfinished business
behind when he's
given a mission.
The re-extermination
has been completed.
-Kazuki.
Kazuki!
[music playing]
-I will not leave your side.
As long as there's
a shred of hope,
I won't give up
until the very end.
The moment you die,
I will die too.
Next time, When Dawn Comes,
I'll splatter your guts.