[music playing]
[roaring]
NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name?
Buso Renkin.
[MUSIC - YOSHIKI FUKUYAMA,
"MAKKA NA CHIKAI"]
NARRATOR: Kazuki, also
known as Victor Three,
faced off against
Captain Bravo, who
had come with a specific
mission, to re-exterminate him.
Both men engaged
in a fierce battle.
And even though Tokiko and
Gouta came to Kazuki's aid,
Kazuki insisted on continuing
to fight his own way.
In the end, Kazuki
was victorious,
and Bravo resolved to entrust
all hope for the future to him.
But then another warrior
chief, the leader
of the Re-extermination
Squad, appeared before them.
His name?
Hiwatari.
-So he managed to survive, huh?
A stubborn fellow, isn't he?
Huh?
How could you get injured
when wearing the Silver Skin?
Don't tell me you screwed
up again, Sakimori.
Who would have thought the
Silver Skin had any flaws, huh?
I guess this means
you're not our ace
in the hole against
Victor now, are you?
-Gouta?
That guy.
-Yeah, I know.
That's no ordinary
pyrokinesis power.
His Buso Renkin is
more than just that.
-I'm going to have to
clean up this mess,
so just get out of
the way, Sakimori.
[gasping]
-Bravo?
-You guys go on ahead.
Let me deal with him.
-So tell me.
What are you intending
to do this time?
-Look, we've known
each other for years.
And you should know by now
that more than anything
in the world, I can't
stand letting kids die.
-Oh, I see.
So I guess you
still haven't been
able to get over that, huh?
Our first and only failed
mission almost seven years ago,
when we both belonged
to the Shosei Squad.
The day that the
elementary school
was completely annihilated.
-It was not completely
annihilated.
[thunder rumbling]
[laughing]
-Totally destroyed.
Damn it, no.
Damn it, why?
Not one survivor.
What a horrendous tragedy.
-I'm so sorry.
I messed up.
It's all my fault.
I'm so sorry.
HIWATARI: All
evidence was destroyed
by a mudslide
caused by the enemy.
We won't know how
many were eaten.
Those who survived were
killed by the mud and rocks.
The enemy has fled.
This is the first time
a mission has failed.
[sobbing]
-Don't give up.
We must protect as many lives
as we possibly can here.
[grunting]
-She's still alive.
She's still alive.
-That doesn't change the fact
that many people died that day,
does it?
You can't continue dragging
it on forever, Sakimori.
We're fighting in
an absurd world.
Let it go.
That's Victor Three
you're standing next to.
SAKIMORI: These kids
are my hope-- the hope
that supported us in the
past and the hope that
will support us in the future.
Hiwatari, just give
these kids a chance.
-Let it go, Sakimori.
If you don't, you'll end
up dead even before I
kill these kids you're
trying to protect.
Do you hear me?
-Dying was my intention after
accomplishing my mission
anyway.
So now that intention has simply
got a different motivation.
I will die to
protect these kids.
-Very well, then.
Your intention is very clear.
And if that's what
you want, I promise
that's what you will get.
However, you won't be
the first one I'll kill.
I'll start with Victor
Three and the traitors.
Buso Renkin of Napalm,
Blaze of Glory!
Eat this!
Ha, ha.
It's a 10,000-degree flame,
burning everything within
a 2,000-foot radius.
In just a matter of
seconds, all of these flames
will have turned
those kids you've
been trying to
protect into ashes.
Isn't that something?
Look at you.
A man who is stronger
than I am shouldn't
be clinging to his past
forever, like you're doing.
Let go of all those memories
from seven years ago
and the memories of
those kids just now.
Huh?
-I'm still alive.
How can that be?
Bravo!
-Eat this!
[gasping]
-Bravo!
What are you--
-Warrior Chief!
-I sure put you guys
through some hard times.
-Bravo, no.
-I'm sorry.
Warrior Tokiko, Warrior
Kazuki, never give up.
-Why, Warrior Chief?
-Captain Bravo, no.
Sakimori.
Bastard!
Yah!
How dare you do that to Bravo?
-Don't get carried away.
If you'd just died sooner,
Sakimori wouldn't have.
Yah!
-What is that?
-It's flame assimilation.
[growling]
-Kazuki!
-So then that's Warrior
Chief Hiwatari's Buso Renkin.
-What is this?
-Eat this.
10,000-degree flame,
Blaze of Glory!
-Energy full blast!
Yah!
-Kazuki!
Uh, the Silver Skin, it's--
-Yah!
Yah!
[gasping]
-Kazuki!
-Huh?
-What the hell?
But Bravo-- Sakimori.
SAKAGUCHI: That's enough.
-Huh?
-Wha-- what is that?
-This is Shosei's Buso Renkin.
-It's Bravo.
-Is that really--
-The Great Warrior
Chief, Shosei Sakaguchi.
-First aid treatment
is complete.
As long as he gets proper rest,
his life won't be in danger.
-Really?
That's great.
-However, even
after he recovers,
he won't be able
to fight as he had.
-That Sakimori was
just so damn reckless.
-Why, you--
-You want a piece of me?
SAKAGUCHI: Cut it out.
-Come on, Shosei,
just let me at him.
-Although it's nice
of you to address me
in such a friendly
manner, please
call me Great Warrior Chief
in front of subordinates.
Unbelievable.
Really.
After seven years, I
thought you both would
have grown up by now.
I left you in charge of things,
thinking you could handle it.
-If I'm in charge, why
do you show up, then?
Seniors should just
retire somewhere,
sipping tea with
their feet-- argh!
[thumping sounds and laughter]
-Uh, excuse me.
-Hmm?
-Can I ask you something?
-Sure, go ahead.
-Why did you, the Great Warrior
Chief himself, come here?
-By any chance, has something
unexpected happened?
-Yes.
Victor was located
again last night.
-Oh.
-We're currently in pursuit
across the Pacific Ocean,
a possible location
for our final battle.
-Frequency from Victor
One has been detected.
The gain is stable, Captain.
It's all clear.
-Enlarge to the main monitor.
SAILOR: Aye-aye.
-This vessel shall
continue its main vigilance
and keep a close
eye on Victor One.
-Aye-aye, sir.
-Aye-aye.
-And so we've been trying to
summon all available warriors.
But when we weren't able
to contact our key people
like Sakimori and the others,
I had a feeling something
was wrong.
Then I come down
here and I see what
I feared most, our
key player, Sakimori,
not being able to fight.
It's a setback, but
we must not miss
this chance for
our final battle.
-Final battle?
SAKAGUCHI: All other
missions are officially
suspended from this moment on.
-Oh.
-From now on, this showdown
with Victor is our top priority.
-What do you mean, "suspended"?
-Do you object?
-Damn right I do.
Given the fact that my target's
standing right in front of me
with a dumb look on his
face, it shouldn't take long
to finish him off
and then move on.
-Go ahead and try.
I'm ready.
Just staring at your ugly face
annoys the hell out of me.
-Bring it on.
-You'll taste the pain
Bravo went through.
-Kazuki, don't.
-Come on, let's go.
-Right where we left off.
[grunting]
-I said missions were suspended.
[shriek]
[thump]
-Kazuki, look out!
-That's got to hurt.
-That is what happens when
you don't follow my orders.
Please don't forget it.
-I won't, sir.
SAKAGUCHI: Now then,
Victor Three, Kazuki Muto.
Due to these circumstances,
your re-extermination
shall be temporarily suspended.
However, that doesn't
mean I can just leave you
on the loose like
nothing's happened.
So therefore warriors Tokiko and
Gouta, I order you both to keep
watch over Kazuki Muto.
-Huh?
-Hey, wait a minute.
Shosei--
-The two of them are not
considered traitors anymore.
-Did you hear that, guys?
Isn't that great news, Gouta?
Don't you think that's
wonderful, Tokiko?
-I guess.
However, that doesn't
change the fact
that you're still in
a difficult position.
-I'm OK with that.
[giggling]
[chopper blades approaching]
-Huh?
-The medical team is here.
KAZUKI: Great Warrior Chief.
-Hmm?
Yes, what is it?
-Don't take this the
wrong way, but please
take good care of Bravo.
-There's no need for you,
an enemy, to ask me that.
Instead, use what is left
of your life, which Sakimori
risked himself to protect,
in a meaningful way.
[chopper engine starting]
HIWATARI: Hey, Shosei.
Aren't you being a little soft?
-I can't take amateurs who
are unable to obey orders
to such an important
and decisive battle.
-But still--
-We may be shorthanded.
But as far as our
human resources go,
we must utilize the right
people in the right places.
-Sakimori's your
favorite, so I understand
you want him to take his
feelings into consideration.
But honestly--
-Are you trying to say
that you don't agree?
-No.
But we do live in an absurd
world with unusual choices,
so I guess we just have to roll
with the punches and improvise.
-You really have grown up quite
a bit, haven't you, Hiwatari?
-Pfft.
-But you are aware of the
fact the word "absurd"
only began to come
out of your mouth
and become a part
of your vocabulary
after that one rainy
day seven years ago?
-Uh.
-It seems Sakimori isn't the
only one who hasn't let go,
doesn't it?
-There's one survivor,
this young girl here.
She's extremely weak.
I don't think she'll
be able to hold out
until a civilian
rescue gets here.
I don't want to let her die.
-Very well.
She will be under the army's
protection for the time being.
We're pulling out.
Let's go, Hiwatari.
[sobbing quietly]
SAKAGUCHI: Hiwatari?
Oh, yes.
And for the record, each and
every one of my subordinates
are favorites of mine.
[sigh]
VICTOR: Alchemist Warriors.
-It appears Victor has
pinpointed our vessel.
He's approaching!
-Submerge quickly.
-Aye-aye, sir.
SAILOR: Victor is
pursuing us underwater.
-All crew, prepare for battle.
-Captain!
-But Captain--
-I'm well aware that the army
underestimates our power.
But no matter how
formidable Victor
may be, if we're in the water,
this submarine's Buso Renkin,
the Deep Breathing, can win.
Send a wire to the
army headquarters.
We will engage Victor.
-Aye-aye.
-Load torpedoes.
CAPTAIN: Line up the bearing.
Now fire!
-Firing.
SAILOR: All shots successful.
-Confirm the target's been hit.
[static crackling]
-Uh.
-Hmm.
SAILOR: Target is unharmed!
-Reload all torpedoes.
-But hold on, sir.
Look over there.
What is that?
-Is that a ghost ship?
-It looks like Victor's
controlling it.
CAPTAIN: Have no fear.
Deep Breathing,
full speed ahead.
Get ready for a deep impact.
-Oof!
CAPTAIN: Damage report!
-The vessel-- hasn't
been damaged at all.
-It can't be.
Gah!
-Oof!
Hey, Captain!
We've lost control
of the vessel.
Something-- some kind of
mysterious power is at work.
-All Alchemist Warriors
will be destroyed.
[laughter]
CAPTAIN: Did you think this
Deep Breathing was just
an ordinary Buso Renkin?
Change!
We can utilize our
three Kakugane together
to create one
powerful Buso Renkin.
-That combination is
the three Kakugane
into six transformations.
-Let's take the sea
aerial battle form.
Formation!
-Battle confirmation.
-Enemy ship right in front, sir.
-Approaching.
-Advance!
Activate drill.
SAILOR: Activating.
-Sir, it worked.
-Well done.
-What?
Where's Victor?
[loud thump]
-Oof!
-All Alchemist
Warriors must die!
CAPTAIN: Send a wire to
the army headquarters.
We could not defeat Victor,
and we will retreat.
-Aye-aye, Captain.
-That's very
unfortunate, Captain.
-Yes, it is.
We didn't even get a
chance to display our four
remaining forms.
[equipment beeping]
-It appears hostilities
have officially begun.
And we have already been
left at a disadvantage.
-We'll just have to
regroup and attack.
-Yes, you have a point.
But the reality is our
battle strength is dropping.
-All right, time to
get moving, you jerks.
Or are you planning on
lying there forever?
-Chief Hiwatari.
-Get up already.
Listen up, ladies.
From now on you're not part
of the Re-extermination Squad.
All members are re-enlisted
into the Victor Hunt Squad.
Let's go.
[whimpering]
-Hey, Busujima.
-Yes?
-It looks like
we're finally going
to be able to use our
combination attack.
-Huh?
Yes, sir.
Please, let's do it.
TOKIKO: I still don't
know who the person was
that appeared
before me back then.
I have no leads.
-A mystery man in an
underground chamber.
It's just one big
enigma, isn't it?
-Yes.
And that's where I
obtained Kazuki's Kakugane.
I'm sure the secret behind
the Black Kakugane is there.
-Bravo sacrificed
himself to save me.
And Victor's still out there,
so we've got no time to waste.
Our destination is the Newton
Apple Academy for Girls.
[MUSIC - AYA KAGAMI, "ITOSHIKI
SEKAI"]
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): The
mystery of the Black Kakugane
is exposed.
The existence of a new
one will be revealed.
If we use that, will Kazuki
be able to return to normal?
Next episode-- a
decision is required.
I'll splatter your guts.