NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
-So what do you want?
Are you on a mission
to eliminate me?
-No, Papillon.
I've come to settle
things-- in Kazuki's place.
-No one could ever
take his place.
Are you saying that Kazuki
Muto is replaceable?
Well, why aren't you answering?
Could someone replace
Kazuki Muto for you?
-Tokiko, where are you?
Look out!
Tokiko!
-Of course, no one
could replace Kazuki.
There is no one in the world
that could ever take his place.
I know that.
But even so, the least I can
do is settle things with you
in his place since he
couldn't do it himself.
So let's end this.
FEMALE VOICE: Activation
device normal.
Pressure device normal.
Heating device normal.
Exactly 60 seconds remaining.
59, 58.
-What is that countdown for?
What's going on?
What is that flask behind you?
FEMALE VOICE 54.
-Don't tell me you're--
-Don't you dare interfere.
-Do you really intend to?
-As I thought before,
maybe it would be best
to burn it all down, and then
create a magnificent world that
suits me, and only for me.
-Tell me. do you
really intend to burn
this world to the ground?
-All I have to tell you is,
I have no interest in a world
without Kazuki Muto.
-Koushaku Chouno!
-How dare you call
me by that name?
Near Death Happiness!
-Tokiko!
-Hm?
Down there, huh?
-Even if Kazuki
isn't here anymore,
this is still the world he
sacrificed his life to protect!
FEMALE VOICE: 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Countdown, 0.
White Kakugane
creation complete.
-Huh?
-You mean that flask was--
-It was built to quickly
create the white Kakugane.
Using Dr. Butterfly and
Dr. Alexandria's technology
as a basis, my master spent
the past month creating it
with every knowledge
and resource available.
My master's only
desire is one thing--
a showdown with Kazuki Muto.
The white Kakugane is
for that purpose alone.
-But Kazuki's not here.
PAPILLON: Have you
given up on him?
Have you given up
completely on Kazuki Muto?
Will you give up on him?
-Kazuki.
Kazuki!
-Kazukit Muto.
Hm?
Is that the moonlight?
No!
That's--
-Could that be--
-Wait.
Is that--
-Great Warrior Chief.
-It's--
BOY: Mahiro!
-Mahiro!
-Look at the moon!
Look!
-The moon?
-Outside.
Outside!
TOKIKO: A beautiful, golden,
yellow-- that's-- Kazuki,
did you know that up close, your
Buso Renkin energy is a bright,
golden yellow color, similar
to the rays of the sun?
-Can it be?
-I'll explain later.
Just come with me right now.
-But why are you here?
-Let's go.
Are you ready?
-Go?
Go where?
-Sakimori will take
the right shoulder.
Hiwatari and Busujima,
take the left.
-Great Warrior Chief,
what's going on?
-You have finally arrived.
You're coming with us.
We're planning to recover
Warrior Kazuki Muto.
-Upper hatch release
has been completed.
-Adjusting a mission angle.
-Confirming heat resistance
and air treatment.
-All clear.
Ready for launch.
-Very well.
Begin launching phase.
BUSUJIMA: Buso Renkin of
Gas Mask, Aerial Operator.
Beginning gas manipulation!
Mixing oxygen.
Injection into rocket pack.
-Blaze of Glory!
Connecting to rocket
pack right now.
-Buster Baron, blast off.
-You still continue to
stand, but the truth
is, this battle has
long been settled.
-No.
Not just yet.
I won't.
I won't give up, no matter what.
Let's finish this, Victor!
I will protect my friends.
And Tokiko too.
No matter what!
I will protect.
I will protect them.
Victor!
-This fight is over.
You must go back to Earth.
Look behind you.
-What is that?
VICTOR: It's your comrades.
They could see that sparkle
of yours from the Earth.
-Victor.
-Over the past month,
they've changed their mind.
They saw that light
and figured out
that you were still
alive out here
and are doing everything
they can to come get you.
That being said, it would be
utterly impossible for those
without bodies like ours
to make it here alive.
You have to go and
meet them halfway.
But in your condition, it's
probably not possible for you
to escape the gravity of
this moon with that lance.
So this is the plan.
I'll use Fatal Attraction to
reverse part of the moon's
gravity and thrust
you into space.
-But Victor, why?
Why are you doing this, Victor?
-Close your mouth, or
you'll bite your tongue.
-Victor, what is this?
-The property of
Fatal Attraction
does not have a direct
effect on my body.
And on top of it, I
don't have enough energy
left to propel the
both of off the moon.
Go.
The people you protected
are awaiting your return.
Now go.
What are you doing?
-No way!
You're coming, too.
Victoria's waiting for you.
If you don't intend to
fight anymore, then let's
search for a new way to
co-exist together, Victor.
Hurry!
-So be it.
It's your funeral.
VICTOR (VOICEOVER): Under
the same circumstances--
[shout]
VICTOR (VOICEOVER): One
man clung to despair.
[shout]
VICTOR (VOICEOVER): While
another wouldn't give up hope.
There is no way despair
could ever defeat hope.
-Dammit, Shusei.
We're not able to
steadily navigate
this rocket engine we
just whipped together.
-The gas jet's fuel is
already at its limit.
-Hold on.
Everyone, be quiet.
Look up ahead in
front of the moon.
-Wait.
Is that--
-Kazuki!
-I can't choose
one or the other!
I will protect us both.
I'll protect everyone.
But who will protect me?
-Kazuki!
SHUSEI: Buster Baron,
approach and acquire.
HIWATARI: That's
easier said than done.
BUSUJIMA: If
something goes wrong,
we could end up killing him.
-This is your mission now.
Bring him home, Tokiko.
TOKIKO: Kazuki.
Kazuki!
KAZUKI: The Silver Skin?
Bravo?
No, it's not.
That's--
-Kazuki!
-Tokiko, it's you!
-When you die,
I'll die with you.
No.
I want to live on with you.
I'll never leave
your side again.
This time for sure.
You and I are one.
BUSUJIMA: Adjusting
atmospheric pressure.
Cooling off heat friction.
WOMAN: Buster Baron
landing complete.
-Papa?
-You OK, Kazuki?
-I think so.
GOTA (VOICEOVER):
Whatever it takes,
I'll do anything, just
to see you smile again.
Just to see you smile again.
I'm really happy
for you, Tokiko.
-Kazuki!
-Huh?
-So you're back, Kazuki Muto!
[coughing]
-Could this be--
-Remember your promise.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
-No.
-Let's settle this
once and for all!
Buso Renkin!
[shout]
-Kazuki!
-Yah!
-Just do it.
And don't mess up this time.
SHUSEI: We made
this by analyzing
the device Papillon left behind.
Please use this.
-Dear Victoria, what
were Alexandria's,
your mother's
final words to you?
ALEXANDRIA (VOICEOVER):
My dear Victoria,
if you should ever
meet your papa,
tell him-- tell him that I
loved him to the very end.
-Great Warrior Chief,
I have a request.
Make me into a Homunculus,
like my daughter.
Homunculi cannot
coexist with humans.
I will take the other Homunculi
and make my way to the moon.
We will dream of the day we
can return to being humans,
and pray that the power of
alchemy is never misused again.
Until then, we'll watch
over the earth from afar.
SHUSEI: All Alchemist
Army activities
will be suspended
for the time being.
Only the research to
change Homunculi back
into humans and the maintenance
of the Kakugane will continue.
All Warriors will surrender
their Kakugane at once.
-I will remain in the army.
This is goodbye.
But I'm warning you, if you
ever make Tokiko cry again--
-No, I won't.
Not ever again.
-That's good.
Then we can always be allies.
-It's time for Jump News.
We're bringing you a
special report today
on the latest urban legend
since the man-faced dog.
Our story is on the much talked
about butterfly man Papillon.
-Papillon?
Yeah, I saw him at the
public bath last month.
-Oh, him?
I guess he's kind of hard
to forget once you see him.
-Yes, he comes to our
restaurant once a week.
Now we have a butterfly
man promotion going on.
Come see for yourself.
-I hear that if you go on a
roof and call his name out--
-The rumor is he's
likely to show himself.
-Yeah!
All right!
Come on!
-As you can see here in Ginsei,
the legend's place of origin,
it's almost like--
-Well, it's hard to explain.
It's like he's
become a local hero.
What is the identity of
the butterfly man Papillon?
And what in the world
are his intentions?
-Hey, Chouno, you gotta
tell me right now,
and you have to be honest
with me-- do you still
want to eat people and burn
this world to the ground?
-I'd heard that you didn't
have any urges for cannibalism.
I guess it's true, then, huh?
-My master's only
desire is one thing,
a showdown with Kazuki Muto.
-Chouno, there is
no point to this.
I don't want to kill you again.
So I've decided
this is the way I'm
going to settle things with you.
Enough with taking
each other's lives.
I wish there was a Buso Renkin
to bring people back to life.
But there isn't such a thing.
So let's mourn for the
lives lost, and put an end
to all this.
PAPILLON: You're e
more of a hypocrite
now than you ever were.
-Whatever you say is fine.
It's certainly much better
than me killing you.
Listen, Chouno,
I'll always remember
your name, no matter what.
I'll always, always
remember who you are.
So please, take your new name,
and your new life, and live on.
ALL: Papillon!
Papillon!
-It's Papillon.
Oh, yes!
Now put more love into it!
ALL: Papillon!
Papillon!
KAZUKI: That Chouno's sure
enjoying himself, huh?
-How are you doing?
Are you feeling OK?
-Yeah, I'm totally fine.
But are you OK, Tokiko?
You seem kind of fidgety
and restless today.
What's the matter?
-Well, the truth
is the Kakugane was
such a big part of
me-- I don't know.
I feel like I'm
missing something.
I'm feeling uneasy right now.
-Well, don't worry.
This Kakugane right here will
always be with you, Tokiko.
Forever.
I promise.
-Is that right?
Then I'll definitely
feel at easy from now on.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): We went
from here to a world of battle,
and came back again.
-Oh, here they come!
I knew they'd be back!
-Kazuki!
[shouting]
KAZUKI: Come on, Tokiko.
[theme music]
-Mahiro Muto's Buso
Renkin seminar.
Hello, everyone.
This is Mahiro Muto.
After introducing all
sorts of Buso Renkin,
today is our last one.
So here is a super
duper Buso Renkin
that's a perfect fit
for our final episode.
And our last Buso Renkin
is the Sunlight Heart Plus.
You already know who this
Buso Renkin belongs to, right?
The wielder is-- yep!
My big brother, Kazuki Muto.
The reason his Sunlight
Heart transformed
was because of his Victor-like
form, which he acquired
through the black
Kakugane, so of course
his Sunlight Heart
evolved as well.
It still takes the
form of a lance,
but the size is more
compact than before.
Kazuki told me the weight
is also much lighter,
and can easily be handled
with just one hand.
However, Kazuki's
favorite energy attack
is still as strong as ever.
The Sunlight Heart
Plus is a Buso Renkin
wit built in energy,
and Kazuki is
able to control its
shape and size freely
by dismantling the lance tip.
Oh, I see.
So the energy isn't in the
decorative cloth, like before.
But Kazuki's energy that
extends far and beyond
still remains the color of
a beautiful sunlight yellow.
Oh, boy.
I remember back when Kazuki
was becoming a victor,
we were all worried about
what was going to happen.
But thanks to the
white Kakugane,
which can neutralize
the black Kakugane,
he's all back to normal.
Pappy was the one who made
Kazuki's white Kakugane, right?
I should remember to thank
him the next time I see him.
A lot has happened,
but no matter
what, my big brother is still
the big brother I've always
known, ever reliable and
always there for everyone!
But I'm telling you, he'd better
not make Tokiko cry again.
So anyway, everyone's now
totally familiar with the Buso
Renkin, correct?
Then let's say you all graduate.
That makes all of you
Buso Renkin masters.
Thank you for watching
'til now, everyone.
I really hope to see
you all again someday!
Bye, bye, bye!