NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
[shouting]
-Let's get out to
of hear to regroup.
-All right.
-Don't think so.
-Take this!
Jousting Flash!
-The boy is skillful
and perceptive.
He's quite impressive.
However, he is still
very inexperienced.
And then there's that girl.
Compared to her
moves the other day,
she now appears to
be rather sluggish.
I can win.
I will win, for the
sake of my master, who
gave me life and power.
[heavy breathing]
-Valkyrie Skirt, standby mode.
-Whoa, that's cool.
Just what I'd expect
from the Valkyrie Skirt.
-I don't really know
what you mean by that,
but if you gain
experience, you'll
also be able to do
all sorts of things.
Hm.
Anyway, wipe off the blood.
Our battle is
definitely not over yet.
-Thanks.
Are you OK, Tokiko?
-Well, actually, my right
shoulder's a little--
-Tokiko?
-I'm OK.
It's really not a big deal.
-Don't push yourself too much.
-Look who's talking.
Who do you think I am?
-An Alchemist Warrior
who's stronger than I am.
But if it's important, then
I definitely speak my mind.
-I see.
All right, then.
I'll be more careful.
But now is the time for battle!
About that hawk
type, it's obvious
that it's in a whole
different league
than the other Homunculi.
His ability to use
those wings as a defense
is not a technique
that came naturally.
-I've found you!
-He's here!
-Just one.
So they've split up, huh?
-Listen up, Kazuki.
The hawk wing defense
is indeed superb.
However, it's not perfect.
When we attacked
simultaneously, he
used his claws, not his wings.
His wing defense
can't completely
handle the succession
of attacks.
There's one thing that will
work-- a high speed multiple
attack.
One of us becomes the
decoy, and the other
delivers the finishing blow.
-All right.
I'll be the decoy.
If I use my lance and combine
the slasher and flash attack,
then I should be
able to keep you
hidden until the last second.
Here I go.
[shout]
BOY: Did you find Kazuki?
MAHIRO: No.
He's not here.
BOY: He wasn't at
the school, either.
-It seems he was
with Tokiko before he
was supposed to meet up with us.
-What?
Her again?
-Yeah.
Ever since Tokiko
showed up, Kazuki
keeps on disappearing
all the time.
-Well, I'm sure glad to
hear he's OK, though.
-Dammit, I'll teach him a
lesson tonight for sure.
MAHIRO (VOICEOVER): Kazuki.
I don't need to worry
about you-- right?
-There's one th that'll work.
A high speed multiple attack.
One of us becomes the
decoy, and the other
delivers the finishing blow!
Hide in the light and
follow me, Tokiko.
-Valkyrie Skirt!
A beautiful golden light.
It's like sunlight.
[shout]
-Huh?
Something's different.
-The wind has changed
from the earlier attack.
-He reads the wind with his
wings, not just his eyes.
-There's a slightly different
wind mixed in this time.
Now I see it.
The girl is hidden
behind the light.
With these claws, I'll take
care of the both of you
at the same time!
-Tokiko!
He figured it out!
Run!
-Kazuki, don't stop!
-I was careless letting
you get above me twice,
but I won't lose!
I'll splatter your guts!
[groan]
[shout]
-Tokiko!
-Kazuki-- do it!
Pierce through!
-Jousting Slasher!
Tokiko!
Why did you do that?
-He figured out our plan.
So I changed it.
But-- argh.
-It's probably the last
chance I had to give my all.
It's finally risen up my spine.
And my body movements are
gradually getting slower.
I didn't want to miss this
chance, so I attacked.
But--
-You're a dangerous woman.
And that tenacity
of yours will surely
mean trouble for my master,
even if you will eventually
become a Homunculus.
So I must finish you
off once and for all.
-It seems that one
more blow is necessary.
-Leave this to me.
You rest, Tokiko.
From here on-- I'm going
to fight by myself.
I'll beat this guy, catch
the Papillon Masked Creator,
destroy the 21st embryo,
and get the antidote.
-There's no point
in acting tough.
Don't you think I know that
the one with inferior fighting
skills is usually the decoy?
I will take care
of you later, boy.
Right now the girl
is my top priority.
-Back off, Kazuki.
Listen to me right now.
You're still no match for him.
-Step aside.
-I will not.
-Fine!
-I will not!
Eve if Tokiko orders
me to, I'm not
backing down no matter what!
[shout]
-An opening.
Jousting Flasher!
No good.
I missed him again!
-No matter how hard
you try, it's useless.
I am able to read the
wind with my wing.
Instead of looking with my
eyes or listening with my ears,
the wind can tell me everything.
No matter what the
situation, my wing defense
will never fail me!
Prepare to die.
WASHIO (VOICEOVER):
Something seems different.
The wind has changed slightly.
A far cry from a
gale or a typhoon,
but I still sense a change.
Even though he is
still inexperienced,
I can feel his
powerful breath now.
The reason must be--
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
This Homunculus--
even if he only has
one arm or one wing,
his defense is as
impregnable as ever.
Kazuki can't do this alone.
-Tokiko, stay out of this.
Here I come!
[shout]
-That girl there--
tell me, is she really
that important to you?
Is it a simple relationship
based on skill hierarchy?
Or is it more than that?
Are you two a couple?
-I owe Tokiko my life.
I died once, and she
gave me a new life.
Now her life is on the line.
I owe her!
No way I'm going to lose to you!
-You and I are the same.
I too owe my life to my master.
Before getting this
body, I was a bird.
A wild hawk.
The ultimate bird of prey,
the champion of the skies.
The strongest of them all.
However-- [gunshot]
I was shot-- either
by accident, or by poachers.
KOUSHAKU: Oh, what a pity.
Well, this is how life goes.
Whether it's a protected species
or not, once you're dead,
you're dead.
But to think I'd come out here
to catch a few butterflies,
and ended up finding
something so rare.
You and I are both
very, very lucky.
Rejoice now.
I'm going to bring
you back to life.
WASHIO: And then
I was resurrected.
I owe my life to my master.
I died once, and he gave
me new life and power.
Now his life is on the line, and
I won't allow you to interfere!
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): No wonder.
His battle skills-- they
come from the instincts
of a wild animal.
-I see.
You and I are the same.
However, our benefactors
are totally different.
Chouno sees all of
you as guinea pigs.
He tramples upon
the lives of others,
thinking only about himself.
Constantly running away
from his fear of death.
What Chouno's doing is
completely wrong, and thanks
to him--
-Silence!
-Kazuki!
WASHIO: Isn't it the
nature of all living
beings to fear of death?
Having lived in the wild,
I relate to this very well.
There is nothing wrong
in my master's actions.
Truth is, you don't want
to die like this, either.
Admit it.
If you pledge never to have
anything to do with my master
again, I could let this
slide, and let you go.
There is nothing shameful
or evil in fearing death,
and running away from it.
-You see, if I run
away, then someone else
will die in my place.
There's no way I will back down.
No way I will lose.
No way I will let
Tokiko die in my place!
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
He's wrapping the cloth
around the tip of his lance.
In that state, he can use
the energy of the cloth,
not just for charging power, but
for destructive power as well.
But that will--
-You're right.
Death is a frightening thing.
I know since I've
died once already,
and Chouno knows it because
he's facing death right now.
But you see, Chouno and
I are both human beings.
That's why there are things
that must not be done,
and things that must
be done even if we die!
-At this rate, he's going
to hurt himself as well.
Stop, Kazuki!
-Here comes energy full blast!
Jousting Crasher!
[scream]
WASHIO: So the breeze has
turned into a real wind.
I know it's selfish,
but I have one request.
My master--
-I won't kill him.
That's not my-- my intention.
I'll just stop him.
-Having heard that,
now I can die in peace.
WASHIO (VOICEOVER):
Die in peace?
I never knew there
was such a death.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Although he said
it was the nature of living
beings to fear death,
he still sacrificed
his life fighting
for the Papillon Masked Creator.
He was a unique Homunculus
until the very end,
and it turned out to be a
good experience for Kazuki
after all.
It's truly unusual to
be able to use the Buso
Renkin to this extent
in just one week.
The fifth day is ending.
There's one more day.
Time will run out tomorrow
night at midnight.
-Tokiko, how are you doing?
We should climb down the
mountain before sunrise.
-Not with your body
in that condition.
It'll just be better to
spend the night here.
It seems that we're quite
deep in the mountains.
We'll rest for the
night and recover
with the healing
power of the Kakugane.
Even if we go down the mountain
tomorrow morning and get
on the train, we probably
wouldn't arrive in Gensei City
until nightfall.
-Then we'll start looking for
Chouno as soon as we arrive.
-I've got a pretty good
idea of his whereabouts.
Now that he's lost his
home and all his Homunculi,
he's nothing but a helpless
high school student.
His last hope is most
likely his family home.
-All right.
Time doesn't run out
until midnight tomorrow.
We have plenty of time!
-Yes, that's right.
I'll stay behind here and
leave all the rest to you.
That's the best thing to do.
-What are you talking about?
That doesn't make sense.
-Don't shake me,
I'm in bad shape.
We're both in bad shape.
Stop it!
-Don't say stuff like that!
-Oh!
-The only way you can make
it in time is by yourself.
Thanks to this, my lower body's
paralyzed and I can't move.
That's why I can't go down
the mountain, you understand?
KAZUKI: But then I won't
have time to come back,
even if I do get the antidote.
-It's OK.
You don't need to
come back anyway.
Tomorrow morning, after you're
gone and I can no longer see,
I'm going to take care of
things by finishing myself off.
[shouting]
-I told you not to
shake me like this.
This way we're both
going to die, now stop i!
-Wait a minute.
This morning you said you
were on a mission, right?
That means you've got friends
and people you can rely on.
-It's useless.
All the Warriors in Japan
are currently out there
on missions of their own.
Unfortunately, even if
I were to ask for help,
it wouldn't show up by
tomorrow at midnight.
I'm sure there'll eventually
be some kind of action
by the main unit.
But it'll only come after
the situation is resolved.
Not too long after this
happens, another warrior
should appear
before you, Kazuki.
Once you report all the
details to that person,
you should bury everything
that happened this week
into the depths of your memory.
You should spend
your days happily
with your sister, and
your friends as well.
You should just go home, Kazuki.
KAZUKI: OK.
I'll go back.
TOKIKO: Good.
That's the way it should be.
-But with you.
-Hey!
Just because I
can't move doesn't
mean you can do whatever
you want with me.
-If we go down the mountain
without waiting for daybreak,
then I'm sure we can get
there before the night falls.
-If you push yourself
like this, you're
gonna drain your
stamina and collapse.
-I'll be OK.
You don't weigh that much.
-You idiot.
That's not the issue.
Let me down.
-Hell no.
I said before that I didn't
want any more victims, remember?
Right now, you happen to
be one of the victims too.
We can do it.
I'll show you that I can
make it there in time.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
His shoulders
are much broader than they look.
NEWSCASTER: The origin
of the gusty winds
that damaged Ginsei High
Dormitory in Saitama Prefecture
in Ginsei City--
-I'm worried.
NEWSCASTER: --is still unknown.
-Kazuki still isn't back.
-I don't know.
Has been disappearing
a lot lately.
But this time he's
been gone a full day.
-Yeah, tell me about it.
During attendance
yesterday, I actually
managed to get away
mimicking his voice.
(KAZUKI VOICE) Hi, guys.
I'm Kazuki.
-Did you actually just do that?
-What kinda freak are you?
-Anyway.
Ever since that Tokiko
showed up in the picture,
Kazuki's weirdness has
kicked into high gear.
Could it be that he's
gotten involved in something
dangerous?
-Well, if that's
the case, then--
MAHIRO (VOICEOVER): Kazuki.
-Big brother!
-Kazuki.
-I'm home.
-Madly in love
and all beaten up?
-What on Earth happened to you?
Were you actually blown away
by yesterday's gusty winds?
-Oh yeah.
That's right.
And Tokiko became unable to move
because of her chronic lower
back pain, so I carried her
on my back the whole way here.
-All the way?
-Yep.
All the way.
-Enough.
Enough already.
Just let me die.
-No negative thoughts!
It's still too soon to give up.
-He is right, Tokiko.
Lower back pain can
be cured, you know.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER): She
is Kazuki's little sister
after all.
-Mhmm.
-All right, everyone.
I need to get going.
-Kazuki, wait!
Where are you off to now?
-Don't worry.
I've just got some
unfinished business.
-But you're all beaten up.
Why don't you just rest
and wait 'til tomorrow?
KAZUKI: No.
It has to be done tonight.
Listen, Mahiro.
I need you to do
something for me.
Take care of Tokiko
while I'm gone.
-What?
-OK?
I'll be back soon, I promise.
-Got it.
Leave it me.
As a matter of
fact, I'm a master
of taking care of people.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
She's pure Kazuki.
A complete female
version of him.
-Wait a second, Kazuki.
What's going on?
Tell us.
Are you hiding
something from us?
What's the deal?
Have you gotten
yourself involved
in something dangerous?
-Sorry.
Okakura.
As you said, I'm involved in
a messy situation right now.
But it's all going to
be resolved tonight.
Everything's gonna be fine.
-Even if you can't tell
us about the situation,
if you need my help, I'm ready.
You know that.
But no worries and no
pressure, all right?
Go and do what you need to do.
-Kazuki, wait.
-What is it, Tokiko?
-Your cell phone is
no longer any use
to you because of the
battle last night,
so take this with you.
Remember to give me a detailed
report on the situation.
And I want you to take this too.
I can't say it will give
you twice the strength,
but two will have stronger
healing powers than one.
You can reduce the
burden on your body
if you apply one to the Buso
Renkin and the other one
to healing.
Kazuki.
You are far better suited
being with your little sister
and your friends than
fighting these battles,
so I want to be completely
sure that you're not
doing this for me.
So come back here
for your own sake,
no matter what
happens out there.
-Understood.
Definitely.
No matter what, I will be back.
KAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
I'll be back, Tokiko.
Everyone.
Just wait for me.
[theme music]
TOKIKO: Kazuki, It's
useless talking to the guy.
He just won't listen
to reason anymore.
all you need to do is take the
Homunculus embryo from him.
Next time, the Butterfly
of a Black Death.
I'll splatter your guts.
-Mahiro's Buso Renkin seminar.
Hey everyone, this
is Mahiro here,
with another round of awesome
commentary on the Buso Renkin.
Since this is our second round
of the Buso Renkin seminar,
my commentary this time
goes to Valkyrie Skirt!
Oh.
Before we get into that,
I think you already
know who wields the
Valkyrie Skirt, right?
Her name, Tokiko Tsumura.
Yep!
That's right!
Tokiko!
She's the person
who gave me brother
a new life after he was
killed by a homunculus.
She's very slender, and
much smaller than I am,
and yet she is a strong
alchemist warrior
who fights and defeat Homunculi.
Ever so cool, she's good
at giving harsh retorts
in response to my
brother's silly comments.
It's a husband and wife
comedy stand up duo.
I'm so jealous of Kazuki because
he gets all the attention.
Oh, but wait!
If the two are
married, then that
makes Tokiko my big sister!
And that means we can do things
like this, and that, and oh!
Oh, what am I gonna do?
I'm so excited!
Oh.
Oops.
I'm so sorry.
My imagination got carried away.
I'll continue that when
I get back to the dorms.
All right!
Back to where we left off.
Tokiko wields and
controls the death
scythe Buso Renkin
Valkyrie Skirt.
Notice the parts
attached to her thighs.
There are four long
thingies sticking out.
The tip of it is
made into a scythe
that can cut almost anything.
Using its manipulators for
quick and precise movements,
Tokiko can take out an
army of enemies at once.
Plus, the manipulators
are directly
controlled by bioelectricity
signals flowing
through her nervous system.
That's why, in order to
relay messages more precisely
and more quickly, Tokiko
attaches them directly
onto her skin.
Even though she
seemed cold to use
and acted really weird
when we first met,
Tokiko is now part of our group.
She's the cool big sister whose
quick wits can put everyone
in their place.
Please take care of my
big brother, Tokiko!
Okie Dokie!
Until next time!