NARRATOR: The supernatural
alloy produced
by gathering the essence
of alchemy is the Kakugane.
This device activates upon a
person's fighting instinct,
manifesting the
possessor's inner power
into a tangible form, creating
a weapon like no other.
Its name, Buso Renkin.
[theme music]
MAN: Yes.
Yes, I understand.
We'll start the
preparations immediately.
We have an urgent mission.
-What is it?
Does it have anything
to do with the young man
we examined before?
-Yes.
While it hasn't been confirmed,
it seems he was disposed of.
-Really?
What a pity.
He was so young.
-We need to recover the black
Kakugane embedded in his chest.
TOKIKO (VOICEOVER):
Kazuki's been--
-The site is Iruka Beach
of Chiba Prefecture.
He will most likely
be discovered
as a drowning victim.
We need to make arrangements
with the local hospital
to recover that black Kakugane.
-Let go of me!
-There's no way
that Captain Bravo
would leave a mission half done.
[groaning]
-This is the energy drain.
-He can't be, even
if he unconscious
and stopped breathing.
But with a black
Kakugane, he can't
be destroyed, even
though he's dead.
-In that case, Kazuki
must still be--
-Tokiko!
TOKIKO: Kazuki.
Kazuki!
Wake up, Kazuki.
Wake up, Kazuki!
Tokiko, that's enough!
The mission must not fail.
He's a certified monster!
If he isn't exterminated, then
irreparable harm may be done.
Buso--
-No.
Don't.
I am the one responsible
for making Kazuki like this.
You want to call
Kazuki a monster,
then you should
call me one, too.
-Damn!
-Gota?
-Drain me, not Tokiko.
Do you hear me?
Drain me!
-It's just as the
Alchemist Army predicted.
The energy drain has absolutely
no effect upon the Silver Skin.
And, in reverse mode, it
is capable of containing
the power, as well.
-Really?
That's most unfortunate.
So then this means that in our
decisive battle against Victor,
you get to be the
ace in the hole.
I'm a bit jealous.
-You shouldn't jump
to conclusions.
This was only a test against
a hypothetical enemy.
It won't necessarily have the
same effect against Victor.
-And that hypothetical enemy.
Was it Kazuki Muto?
Why did you leave his
body in the ocean?
Don't tell me that you did
that to let him get away.
-Don't underestimate
me, Hiwatari.
I felt his death
with this very first.
There's no doubt that
I killed Kazuki Muto.
-I shall lead the unit
to recover the Kakugane.
You shouldn't make any
unnecessary moves, Sakimori.
-Don't you call me by that name.
-Haven't you received
orders to return to base?
Then you should return
to army headquarters
and await the report.
PAPILLON: How did
you find this place?
-I was in charge of
the computer network
at Dr. Butterfly's
secret LXE base,
so I was able to find this
place when I hacked it.
-Hm.
If I remember correctly,
didn't the Alchemist Army
take you into their protection?
Have you come to
defeat me in order
to earn some points with them?
-My Kakugane's been
confiscated, so I'm powerless.
I have come here for
Kazuki Muto's sake.
Papillon, I've come to ask you
to save Kazuki Muto's life.
-Hm.
Oh, really?
Well then, let's hear
what you have to say.
-Oh, no.
I must have passed out.
For how long?
Kazuki?
Kazuki--
-I'm sorry.
Dying and coming back to
life, coming back to life
only to die again.
I'm always causing you trouble,
but there won't be a next time.
-Kazuki.
-I've hacked into
the army's computers.
Kazuki Muto's condition
is now at stage one.
In roughly six weeks he
will reach stage two.
At that time, he is
expected to transform
into being identical
to the first Victor.
Kazuki Muto is now being
referred to as Victor Three.
He is to be eliminated
swiftly and quietly in order
to recover the black Kakugane.
-Oh, dear.
He really is in a
tough spot, isn't he?
-Are you really as
indifferent as you seem?
If we let matters
continue this way,
then Kazuki will
surely be killed.
Surprising.
I was under the
impression that you
wanted to kill Kazuki yourself.
-What are you getting at?
-I want you to help Kazuki.
-Ah.
-I'm serious about this.
You yourself are scheming
to become a Victor,
isn't that right?
Wouldn't it be good for you to
have a sample close at hand?
-Hm.
But of course.
-Saving Kazuki from
the Alchemist Army
is not a bad proposition from
your point of view, either.
-Ah-ha!
But no.
I love using other
people for my benefit,
but unfortunately
for you, there's
nothing I hate more than
being used by others.
And I don't
appreciate the way you
are trying to manipulate
me, while you yourself
do nothing about the situation.
-If I could do
something, I would.
But I'm still
recovering, and I'm
powerless without a Kakugane.
There's absolutely nothing
I can do to help him.
-A genuine Kakugane,
serial number 70.
The one that Dr.
Butterfly was using
before his untimely passing.
You say you have no power?
What about the ability
to elicit information
from the Alchemist Army?
Or your devious
plans on using me?
Infiltrate the army
and gather information.
I will be the one who uses you.
-Well, it looks like
I will be the one who
gets used, after all.
Buso Renkin.
-Angel Gozen is back again
as an alternate type!
But I'm not so sure
I like this new look!
-Oh, my.
-Stylish, don't you think?
So, then you say
he's at Iruka Beach?
KAZUKI: FOr the
next six weeks, I
intend to keep fighting on as
a human being, to the very end.
-I see.
But what exactly do the words
fighting to the very end mean?
-I'm not sure, but
you're not exactly
offering me any other advice.
-The black Kakugane
embedded in your chest--
I recovered it from a previous
mission before we met.
-That's right.
I remember you telling me that.
You came to this place
right after completing
a previous mission
at another school.
-If we return to that
school and investigate,
we might figure out
a way of dealing
with the black Kakugane.
-Then I'm going to go there.
-I can't let you
go alone, Kazuki.
I'm going with you.
-You can't.
If you go with me, then
you'll be branded a traitor.
-I don't care.
I'm not leaving your side.
-Tokiko.
TOKIKO: I know what
you're thinking, Kazuki.
If six weeks passed and
everything were to go in vain,
you would probably kill
yourself, wouldn't you?
Well, I can't let that happen.
For the next six
weeks, you and I
shall be of one mind and body.
If you're going to die, then
I'm going to die with you.
You understand?
-I'm not going to die.
And I won't let you
die either, Tokiko.
-Kazuki.
What's wrong with your hand?
Let me take care of it.
-Thanks, Tokiko.
-Oh, that's right.
Gota.
Gota!
Gota?
[laughing]
TOKIKO: What are
you laughing about?
On your feet, Gota.
If you can't pass the
survival training,
then you'll never
make it as a Warrior.
-I've had it, Tokiko.
I'm too tired to go on.
-Get up.
If you don't, then I won't be
able to tend to your wounds.
So, why were you
taken in by the Army?
-I've been told
that my family was
slaughtered by the Homunculi.
-What do you mean?
-I don't remember a thing.
I was just a baby
at the time, so I
don't have any memories
about my family
or the Homunculi
that killed them.
As far back as I can remember,
I've been in an orphanage run
by the Alchemist Army,
and apparently someone
thought I possessed the
qualities to be a Warrior,
so here I am.
But after all, I guess I don't.
-Is that so?
But what if one day you
actually find something you feel
is worth fighting for?
Someday, there may be
something you want to protect.
Now's your chance to get
stronger and be ready,
so when that day arrives
you'll not be powerless,
nor will you be sorry
that you toughed it out.
Now get up, Gota.
-I can't do it, Tokiko.
-On your feet.
-Huh?
Warrior Chief Hiwatari?
-Your mission was to detain the
female Alchemist Warrior Tokiko
Tsumura, but I don't
see her with you.
Did you fail?
Don't tell me-- she's with
Kazuki Muto right now,
isn't she?
So he's still alive, is he?
Then lead me to him.
I shall exterminate Kazuki Muto,
also known as Victor Three,
and then the traitor
known as Tokiko, as well.
-But wait a minute!
We don't really know if she
really betrayed us or not.
-You told her how dangerous
Victor Three is, didn't you?
If she insists on protecting
him, then she's a traitor.
It's about time
you guys showed up.
What took you morons so long?
-Ikusabe, Negoro
reporting for duty.
-Time to mobilize the
re-extermination squad.
Our mission is to
destroy Victor Three,
and there appears to be a
traitor with him as well.
IKUSABE: But aren't
they just mere children?
HIWATARI: We still need
to dispose of them.
He may be incomplete,
but he is a Victor.
-Someday there may be
something you want to protect.
So when that day arrives
you'll not be powerless,
nor will you be sorry
that you toughed it out.
-Well, w you waiting for?
Hurry up and take me to them.
-No.
-What?
-I don't care what she did.
I won't help you kill Tokiko.
I won't do it!
-What do you think you're doing?
Have you lost your mind?
It's three against one.
You may be a rookie,
but surely you
must realize how stupid this is.
-If you're such
a combat veteran,
then why are you just
talking, and not fighting me?
-Heh.
Pretty confident.
-Buso Renkin!
-Hm?
-Empty handed?
-Was that remote demolition,
or was it telekinesis?
No, that's not it.
It appears that you launched
some small, high speed
weapon that circled around
beyond our field of vision
to strike from the sides.
-Buso Renkin of
Chakram, Motor Gears!
-What's a chakram?
-It's an Indian thrown weapon.
-Pretty clever.
He destroyed our means
of transportation
while simultaneously creating a
smokescreen with the explosion.
-And all the commotion will
surely draw a curious crowd.
-First a sneak attack, and now
you dare face me in a battle?
Bring it on.
GOTA (VOICEOVER): So that's
Warrior Chief Hiwatori's Buso
Renkin.
-He looks like he's
planning to escape,
using the chakram as a decoy.
-Warrior Chief, there's a
fire station three miles away.
They'll be here in
about 10 minutes.
-Heh, heh, heh.
-As I expected.
-But he won't get
away that easily.
-Motor Gears, Skywalker Mode!
If I defeat him, I'll be
able to protect Tokiko!
[shout]
-Looks like I got him.
-You think so, huh?
Think again.
[scream]
HIWATORI (VOICEOVER):
The ocean lies below?
-Are you OK?
-What happened to
that little punk?
-He's fled.
[sirens]
-Warrior Chief--
-Pull back, and leave no trace!
GOTA (VOICEOVER): That attack
should have killed him.
What on earth can
his Buso Renkin be?
And what are its
characteristics?
Tokiko!
[shout]
-Stretch.
Contract.
Stretch.
Stretch some more.
[shout]
-Believe it or not, I am a
master at hypnotic suggestion.
All right, what's next?
-Twist.
Twist.
-Twist some more.
Hey.
Good morning.
-What are you guys doing
this early in the morning?
BOY: Kazuki, that was
your idea, wasn't it?
-It wasn't me, it
was all those--
-Stop fooling
around and be quiet.
People are trying to sleep.
Good, they're still sleeping.
There's my luggage.
-We caught you, Tokiko!
-Ha.
-Where'd you slip out to?
-Were you at strawberry's?
-That's a no no!
-You need to be punished.
-What are you doing?
Be quiet, or you're gonna
wake up the other guests!
-Shh!
-By any chance, is
it another mission?
-Well, something like that.
-In that case, I guess
we shouldn't ask you
for the details.
-We'd appreciate
it if you didn't.
Just so you all
know, this time we
might be gone for
up to six weeks.
-Six weeks?
So we won't see you
until the new semester?
-You're giving up your vacation?
Being a hero sure is tough.
-Just make sure you take
good care of Tokiko.
-Be careful and watch
out for yourselves.
-Good luck to the both of you.
-Here.
Take this, an umbrella.
There's only one, but
you guys can share it.
-We'll see you
guys next semester!
-Sure.
-See you soon.
-It looks like they're
both injured, doesn't it?
-Yes, it does.
-I wonder if pretending
not to notice
was really the
right thing to do.
-It's better that way.
I'm telling you.
-Are you all right?
-Oh, don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
-Let's go, Kazuki.
-Yeah.
We'll go.
And we're coming back for sure.
I promise.
MAN: The fire spread to
the two cars and one house,
but no human casualties.
-We must make sure
that no civilians
are harmed in our mission.
-I wonder how long we
can keep things that way.
-I'm not sure.
-Follow that rookie.
I have no doubt he's going
to meet up with the traitors.
-With proper training, he'd
probably make a fine Warrior.
-No.
We'll make sure he
gets properly killed.
-Warrior Chief.
-My way of doing things
is to use absurdity
to force the absurd
into submission.
Contact headquarters.
Tell them that
Sakamori has failed,
and that I shall proceed
with the mission.
-This is where I fought
Bravo last night.
I never imagined we'd
end up in this situation.
You and Bravo were my
only fellow Warriors.
I just wanted the three of us
to carry out the next mission
together.
-Well now it's
just the two of us.
-Yeah.
I guess we'll just have to
get used to fighting as a duo.
-Gota!
-Tokiko.
-Re-extermination squad,
and Warrior Chief Hiwatari?
-Gota, you should go
back to headquarters
and turn yourself in.
You'll still have to
face disciplinary action,
but at least you
won't be killed.
-No.
I'm coming with you.
We're in this together.
-Huh?
GOTA (VOICEOVER): The
re-extermination squad
also has Tokiko
on their hit list.
I'm going with you.
-Tokiko told me what you
did for me last night.
Thanks, Gota.
-Be careful!
Let me see your hand.
I'll tend to your injuries.
-It's OK.
I already took
care of it myself.
-Just let me see.
I overdid it last night.
I'm sorry.
-Looks like we both
hurt the same hand.
Anyway, what do you say?
-Huh?
Honestly.
The two of you are acting
like a bunch of little kids.
I'm going to withdraw
some money from the ATM
before our accounts are frozen.
Wait here.
-I just want to be clear that
I'm not doing this for you.
The truth is, I don't
care what happens to you.
I don't even care
what happens to me.
All I want is to protect
Tokiko at all costs.
-You know what?
I think I'm gonna get
along with you after all.
-Huh?
-We should shake on it.
-I don't think so.
-OK, I was still able
to make a withdrawal.
We shouldn't have to worry
about money for a while.
Careful.
If your hand gets wet,
your wound won't heal.
-Oh.
-Excuse me.
-All right, let's go.
-Gota, stop pushing.
-Should we buy another umbrella?
-No, we're fine like this.
-Hey!
I'm receiving a message
from undercover agent Ouka!
What is it?
What?
Be happy, Pappy!
Kazuki's still alive!
-Hm?
Just as I thought.
[gasp]
-Are you OK?
-I just felt a monstrous chill.
What happened?
Angel Gozen.
Angel Gozen!
-I know we arrived a bit
late, but after all, we've
come all the way to the beach.
It would be a shame not to show
off my super fabulous swimsuit.
The Alchemist Army may know
more about the black Kakugane,
but when it comes to Muto, I
know far more than they do.
He'll never give up, and
won't be so easy to kill.
I estimate 41 days
until Kazuki Muto
ceases to be a human being.
[theme music]
TOKIKO: I'm sure if
we go to the place
where I found that Kakugane,
we'll learn something.
I'll cure Kazuki.
And to do that, I'll defeat
anyone who stands in our way,
no matter who they are.
Next time, The Escape.
I'll splatter your guts!
-Mahiro Muto's Buso
Renkin seminar.
Hello, there.
This is Mahiro Muto.
For this seminar, I'll
be a bit more serious
as introduce
today's Buso Renkin.
Even I take things
seriously once in a while.
Oh, no, no, no!
I mean, I always take
things seriously.
Now then, for our
sixth seminar, let
me introduce Victor's Buso
Renkin, the Fatal Attraction.
Thanks to the work
of Dr. Butterfly,
Victor, the former
Alchemist Warrior,
has awakened from
his long slumber.
I don't know all the
details, but Victor,
who has a black Kakugane,
embedded within his chest,
is supposed to be a third entity
that surpasses both Homunculus
and humans.
And a black Kakugane
is something
that the Alchemist Army
came up with 100 years ago,
in an attempt to create
the Philosopher's Stone.
It's a very scary thingy
that causes the user's power
to go out of control
and bring destruction.
On top of that, it brings
death to all living beings
by sucking away its life force.
That time when the Homunculi
attacked Ginsei Academy
and Victor awakened, all of us
felt our strength leaving us.
I thought for sure
that we were done for,
but that was all because
of Victor's energy drain.
Victor's Buso Renkin
is a giant axe
that is activated from
the black Kakugane.
Simply put, the giant
axe emits a power
called the Fatal Attraction.
But what's amazing is that
it can control gravity.
Whatever attack it takes will
be cancelled out by shifting
the gravitational
power and direction.
And it will destroy things
by twisting and warping it.
Everything gets squashed.
How scary!
Everyone thinks that
Victor is completely evil.
But you know, it
seems like he's had
a very tragic past, as well.
Oh, I really hope my big brother
can resolve everything soon,
so everyone can live
happily ever after!
Okie dokie, see you next time!