♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies and
gentlemen, this is the final lap
of the Great Eastern
Central Grand Prix.
[ANNOUNCER] And here they
come around the final turn!
Number 12 is in the lead,
but Speed in the Mach 5
is challenging for
the winning position.
[ANNOUNCER]
Speed Racer is pulling ahead!
He's out in front!
And here he comes
toward the finish!
The flag is waved!
Speed Racer wins!
[CROWD cheering]
[NARRATOR] Later that day,
at the International Airport.
[THUG A]
Go!
[BOTH gasp]
[TRIXIE]
Where'd those shots come from?!
[SPEED]
I don't know!
[BOTH gasp]
Someone tried to
shoot us, Trixie.
I wonder why and who they were.
If we try to find out, we'll
miss the plane for Hawaii
and you won't get there
in time for the race!
[SPEED]
You're right. Come on.
You've failed, hmm?
[BOTH]
Sorry.
[MAN] You're not supposed
to fail. Come over here.
Fools!
You must pay for
your failures...
[BOTH]
Wait, please! Not the cigar!
[MAN] Yes, the one
with the poison needles.
[BOTH]
Please don't use it, Omar!
--[thud]
--[THUGS whimpering]
[BOTH groaning]
[WOMAN]
Speed.
Welcome to Hawaii.
[SPEED]
Gee, thanks.
C'mon, Speed. They're checking
the Mach 5 through customs.
[yells]
[SPEED]
Well?
[OFFICER]
Hmm...
[TRIXIE] Haven't you finished
checking it through yet?
We're in a hurry!
It's my duty to
check it carefully!
[SPEED]
Well, check it all you want.
You won't find
anything suspicious.
[OFFICER]
Mm, no?
And what is this if
it's not suspicious?
What a surprise, Speed!
[SPEED]
It's Spritle and Chim Chim!
Please come with me
to the office right now.
[BOTH gasp]
[SPEED]
Uh-oh...
C'mon, you, too!
[SPRITLE] I didn't do anything
wrong! Put me down, let me go!
--Spritle!
--Chim Chim!
[TRIXIE]
Come back here!
--[SPEED] Hey! Spritle, wait!
--[TRIXIE] Don't run away!
[SPEED]
Huh? Where'd they go?
Bye-bye, Speed!
--Hey, come back!
--Where are you going, Spritle?!
Sightseeing! And I'll bet
we'll see all of Hawaii
before they even
get started, huh?
[SPRITLE]
Whee!
[SPRITLE laughs]
[SPRITLE] Oh look, Chim Chim,
isn't that Waikiki Beach?
Them!
[yelling]
I'm their target again!
What'd we do wrong
this time, huh?!
[gunfire]
Okay! This should stop them!
[screams]
So he's a wise guy.
Chim Chim, what's going on?!
We're going to crash! Ah!
[tires squeal]
Well, did you find it?
No, right. He doesn't
have it on him.
He doesn't? That means
the girl must have it.
We'll have to get it from her.
We must get our hands on it.
[THUG C]
You're right, Mr. Slimer.
[SPRITLE] We've got to
find out what they're up to.
And there's only
one way to do that!
We'll find out where
their headquarters is.
Let's sneak into the trunk of
that car over there and hide.
And now there are
some other people
that we've got to take care of:
A young racer
and his girlfriend.
They shouldn't have run off.
I wonder where they are.
[TRIXIE] Look, Speed! There's
something burning up ahead!
[TRIXIE]
That's the car Spritle was in!
Oh! Look!
I can see it's too late
to do anything for him!
Well, that's the same man we saw
back in that airport
with the girl.
I wonder what's happened to her.
And I'll bet they were the
ones being shot at, not us.
Sure, that's it, Trixie. Someone
was trying to get rid of 'em,
and we got in the line of fire!
I wonder if they
caught Spritle...
I certainly hope not. And yet,
he disappeared, didn't he?
I'll bet he has been captured!
Wait a minute!
Look, Speed!
[SPEED]
Hmm?
A roll of film! Where was it?
[TRIXIE]
In these flowers!
I think maybe this is what
those men are looking for.
Trixie, I'll be back
later. Stay here.
You were right! The young racer
just walked into the library,
and now he's
talking to the clerk.
[CLERK]
Can I help you?
May I use your microfilm reader
for just a few minutes?
[CLERK] The microfilm reader?
Of course. This way.
Here you are, and you may
take your time with it.
Thank you.
[SPEED] Hmm... Looks like
some kind of design...
But what is it, anyway?
I can't figure it out.
[THUG D]
Can't you?!
[SPEED]
Huh?!
[chuckles] I'll tell
you what it is,
it's the design for
the latest laser gun
that shoots a powerfully
destructive laser ray.
The design covers the
most important part
of the laser beam ray gun.
[SPEED]
Now I understand everything!
Don't get smart! It's
none of your business!
Just what're you planning
to do with the film?
[THUG D]
Wouldn't you like to know?
But then, you know
too much already.
[SPEED]
Huh...?
[THUG D] I'll make sure your
mouth is shut permanently!
Too bad you had to butt in
where you didn't belong!
[yells]
[THUG D] The light's
in my eyes! I can't see!
[gasps]
I ran into a trap!
[THUG D] You didn't think
you'd get away, did ya?
Nobody gets away from us.
Too bad you had to try
being such a smart kid,
because it's not gonna
make it any easier.
Too bad! [chuckles]
Now give me that
there roll of microfilm!
[THUG D]
A wise guy, huh?!
Hand me it!
[chuckles]
He was about to
pull the trigger.
[SPEED]
You're a girl!
Wait, I met you at the airport!
[WOMAN]
You have a good memory, Speed!
I put a string of flowers
around your neck.
My name's Kana. Tie him up.
[SPEED]
Okay.
Well, that takes care
of one of them,
but there are some more of them.
Hmm? Kana? Where are you?
--[engine revving]
--Kana! Kana! Kana!
[SPEED]
I wonder why she ran away.
And she must've taken
that film with her.
But she wouldn't have helped
me if she were one of them.
[THUG E]
Stop! Stop your car!
[gasps]
[THUG E]
Okay, now get out.
[gasps]
Kana!
Huh?!
[laughs] He drove right off
the highway into the ocean,
so we're not gonna be
bothered by him anymore!
[laughs]
Now which way?
Wait, stop, young man!
You mustn't come this way,
it's too dangerous!
[SPEED]
Dangerous?
A dragon lives within
that mountain.
[SPEED]
Hmm?! There's no such thing!
The stranger just pulled away
from here. I couldn't stop him.
He had to be lying.
Dragons aren't real. Not today.
[whirring]
Huh?
There was a sound. It was weird.
[whirring]
What was that in there?
What are they
building down there?!
[THUG F]
Don't move!
[SPEED]
Huh?!
[THUG F]
On your feet!
All right...
This is Point 8. Speed
Racer just broke away!
You must stop him!
[SPEED gasps]
[screaming]
[KANA]
Speed...
[SPEED groans]
[KANA]
Speed.
Oh, it's you, Kana.
[groans]
[SPEED]
W-Where are we? Huh?
[KANA]
In a dungeon. We're prisoners.
We are?
It comes back to me now.
I fell off a cliff.
They captured me, I guess,
when I was beneath the sea.
Then they brought me in here.
Well, you're awake now, Speed.
Why am I locked up?
Because you stuck your nose
where it didn't belong!
But it doesn't matter,
because we got the microfilm
from that Secret Service girl.
Kana's in the Secret Service?!
[OMAR]
That's right!
She works for the International
Secret Service. Didn't you know?
You're lucky we
took you prisoner.
Now you can participate in
the experiments we're planning
with the laser beam.
You're going to be
our first guinea pig.
You wouldn't dare
try to do that!
You mean you'd test
that laser beam on me?!
[OMAR]
That's exactly what I mean!
I won't cooperate!
I don't think you
have much choice!
We'll conduct the
test tomorrow morning.
[SPEED] You won't get away
with it! I'll see to that!
[OMAR]
Heh!
[KANA] Those evil men
will do as they say.
I'm sorry I got you into this.
That's all right.
The important thing is
for us to get out of here
before tomorrow morning.
But how are we going to do it?
[SPRITLE]
It's quiet out there now.
[gasps] Ooh...
[SPRITLE] Where are we, anyway?
Looks like a garage.
It's the Mach 5! Speed must
be here! We'll look for him!
First, let's get
something to eat!
Oh...
There's nobody in sight, but we
better be careful, Chim Chim!
[SPRITLE] Oh! There's a guard!
But he's asleep.
Chim Chim, go look around.
See if you can find any food.
[babbling]
There's food? There's food
inside that room? Good!
[GUARD]
What's going on...?
[SPRITLE]
He's waking up! Hit him!
Huh? Could that be Spritle?
Spritle! What're
you doing here?!
[SPRITLE]
Speed! We found you!
[gibbers]
Use the guard's key
and get me out, Spritle!
I'll have you out of
there in a minute! Hmm.
Ha! There you are!
I did it! [laughs]
[SPEED]
Kana, let's go!
C'mon, Speed,
you'd better hurry!
[THUG G]
Hold it!
Heh, heh! Sorry, but
no one's going anywhere!
[THUG G chuckles]
We can't get away!
You're right.
We won't shoot now.
We'll take care of ya
tomorrow with the laser ray.
[THUG G] After that, you won't
cause us anymore trouble.
See ya tomorrow.
What're they gonna
do with us, Speed?!
[SPEED]
We'll find out in the morning...
This morning, we brought the
laser gun for its first tests.
When we built it, we followed
the design on the microfilm.
Watch!
[BOTH gasp]
Wow!
Now, I want all of you
to stay right there!
We've seen how well the laser
gun works on a stone wall,
now we'll see if it
works against humans!
Remember our plan...
Okay...
[KANA]
Please, let us go!
I can't! You know too much!
[SPEED]
Run!
Hey, wait!
This way, Speed! Hurry!
[explosion]
[SPRITLE] Hey, Speed,
over here! C'mon, look!
Here's the Mach 5!
Quick, everybody, hop in!
[ALL gasp]
Heh. You thought you
managed to get away,
but you'll never
be able to escape!
This tank is equipped
with a new laser gun!
Now, you shall be destroyed!
[gasps]
[KANA] How're we going to get
around these craters, Speed?!
[SPEED]
I don't know yet!
They're going to fall right
into one of those craters...
...unless I get them
with the laser.
Faster!
They've gone far enough!
Now I'll give them
a blast of the laser
that will finish
them off for good!
[PILOT A] Hey, one of the laser
cannons was just smashed!
And another!
Y-- What's that?!
Get it! Before
that robot gets us!
They got it! It was
caught in the beam!
Now, destroy the car and
everybody inside of it!
[SPRITLE]
Hurry!
Faster!
[KANA, SPRITLE scream]
[SPEED]
Hang on!
[BOTH gasp]
Do something!
[BOTH scream]
[ALL gasping]
We almost didn't make it!
[SPEED]
Uh-huh.
Well, those men didn't, but
they paid for what they did.
They paid for their crime.
[NARRATOR] See the next exciting
episode of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪