♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR] Speed has learned
that mysterious forces
are after a Model T engine with
a secret number etched on it.
Now with the owner
of that engine,
he has drawn those mysterious
forces out into the open.
But under the command
of Tongue Blaggard,
they are out to get him.
[gasps]
[THUGS screaming]
[NARRATOR] Rex, secretly
Speed's older brother
who ran away from
home years ago,
is ready to protect Speed.
[RACER X] I've got to slow them
down so Speed can get away.
[screams]
[RACER X] That'll keep them
out of mischief for a while.
[SPEED] I wouldn't be
here in danger right now
if I hadn't stopped the Mach 5
yesterday to help Mr. Clepto,
uh, kind-hearted old
Mr. Light Fingers Clepto, Jr.,
to get the top up on
his ancient Model T,
the same car that
was left to him
when his father was shot down
by gangsters years ago.
Mr. Clepto and his
granddaughter, Suzie,
gave me dinner at his home,
where I met all his
adopted children,
and where he showed me how he
took care of the ancient Model T
his father had left to him.
He also showed me the old
engine he took out of the car.
The engine the mysterious
forces were now looking for.
[THUGS screaming]
[THUG A]
Get out of the way!
Now, talk. Who gave you
the orders to attack me?
Who's behind this whole
thing? Come on, talk!
[SPEED gasps]
I'll bet the boss is up there.
[BLAGGARD] Right, sonny.
Now let go of my man.
[SPEED]
Who are you?
[BLAGGARD]
Heh, heh! Look behind you.
[SPEED gasps]
[TINY yells]
[CLEPTO]
Speed! Speed, wake up, Speed!
[gasps]
It's a fine mess
we're in, Speed.
[SPEED]
Where are we?
[CLEPTO]
Who knows? But I don't like it.
Just look around.
[CLEPTO]
That's a Model T just like mine.
And it's in mint condition! Uh!
That is my car!
I'm more interested in
finding out where we are
and how we might be able
to get out of here.
Ah!
This might be a way out!
[BLAGGARD cackling]
Old man, you are
Light Fingers Clepto, Jr.,
the son of Light Fingers Clepto.
What?! How'd you discover that?
I've got a spy network
throughout the world.
I find out everything
worth finding out.
You're nothing but a thief!
You stole my precious Model T!
I always get whatever I want.
Now tell me, what did you
do with the original engine
that was in the car?
[CLEPTO]
Why should I tell you?
What're you planning
to do with it?
I don't plan to do
anything with that engine
except read the
secret numbers on it
because they'll tell me where
a billion dollars in gold
was hidden by your father!
What?! A billion in gold?
[BLAGGARD]
That's right!
That's why I busted out
of Sung Along Prison,
so I could get my
hands on that loot.
Then you must be the escaped
convict, Tongue Blaggard!
Right! Now tell me where
the Model T engine is
or Tiny goes to work.
[BOTH gasp]
I'll never tell you where
that engine is! Never!
Tell me!
Don't hit him! I'll
tell you where it is!
No! Don't tell him
anything, Speed!
Tell us!
[CLEPTO]
No, Speed, don't!
The engine doesn't
exist. I destroyed it.
You destroyed it, eh?!
But I remember the numbers!
[gasps]
Let's go to Misty Valley and
split up the loot three ways.
We'll be glad to share it.
If you won't share it, I won't
tell you what was on the engine,
so think it over, Mr. Blaggard.
Think it over carefully.
I wouldn't share anything
with a man like that.
[SPEED]
Shh!
I was just trying
to save us from Tiny.
The first chance we get,
we'll turn Blaggard and
his gang over to the police
and you'll be able to keep
that billion for yourself.
Well, the treasure did
belong to my father,
so now it's rightfully mine.
But I'm willing to give
you enough money
so that you'll be able to
enter the Multi-Peak Race!
[SPEED]
Shh!
I accept the deal to
split it three ways.
It's late and Speed
isn't home yet.
I suppose he's still training
for the Multi-Peak Race.
He must love training.
[phone rings]
[POPS]
Hello?
Oh, hello, Speed!
What's that? You're going
for a long ride with a friend
and you won't be
home until tomorrow?
Well, that's all right, I guess.
Good work, Speed.
Tell Trixie the ring I wanted
to get for her costs over $650,
so she might as well forget it.
I'll have to get
a lot more money
before I'll be
able to afford it.
Okay, you've said enough, kid.
Speed's having a little
trouble about pocket money.
He should know the
money troubles I have.
He's talking about paying
for a ring for Trixie.
He must be kidding.
We haven't even enough money to
send him to the Multi-Peak Race.
[laughs]
They're guarding us in
the front and in the back.
We won't have a chance
to call the police.
Don't worry, Mr. Clepto.
I sent out a code signal to
Trixie to start looking for me,
and now I'll talk
to her by radio.
Trixie, come in.
Wait. Something's wrong.
Some tubes are missing.
The radio won't work.
At the rate we're goin',
we won't reach Misty Valley
before midnight.
Why hurry? We'll spend the
night at that lodge up there.
[THUG A]
Good idea, Boss!
[snoring]
Hey! Wake up!
The racer kid skipped out!
[THUGS chattering]
[BLAGGARD]
Tiny!
[TINY grunts]
Shall we take a little
midnight stroll out there?
[RADIO] Hello. Hello.
This is the police.
Who's calling and where?
[SPEED]
Forget it.
Checking up to see if
your car's all right?
You're a very conscientious kid.
[SPEED]
Oh-- I, uh-- That is, I--
This steering wheel's
got lots of buttons on it.
Let's see...
That's the automatic jack.
It raises the car several
feet so it can be serviced.
What's this for?
The B stands for "belt tires"
for driving in mountain areas.
That's a groovy idea.
Hey. Which button
is for the weapons?
Sorry, but the Mach 5
doesn't carry them.
It was built for racing
driving and that's all.
[BLAGGARD]
Hm...
And what's this button here?
[SPEED] That's for a
remote-controlled homing robot.
Is this the remote control?
Yes, but please don't fool
around with the homing robot.
[BLAGGARD chuckles]
It's like playing
with a toy airplane.
I haven't had this much
fun since I was a kid.
Fly up! Down!
What's this? I'll try it.
[SPEED]
Uh-uh, don't touch it.
Crazy, that homing
robot can really fly.
[BLAGGARD chuckles]
Now it's gone!
[SPEED] It's on its way
home to the family,
but they won't know where I am.
If only I'd been able
to give the homing robot
a message to carry.
[bell ringing]
[POPS]
All right!
Take it easy; I can
hear ya ringing the bell.
Who can it be at
this time of night?
Oh! Trixie!
Speed was supposed to take
me to a party tonight,
but he stood me up!
He never showed up at all!
Where is he? I wanna give
him a piece of my mind!
[POPS]
Hm...
That's funny,
he phoned me this afternoon to
tell me he was going on a trip.
He told you he was going away?!
But he gave me
a message for you.
He said you can
forget about the ring.
Forget about the ring, Pops?
He said it costs over $650,
so at least for now,
you might as well
forget about the ring.
Over $650?
Wait just a minute!
What're you so excited about?
Pops, that message was a code!
What do you mean a code?
And a couple of zeros
and it indicates the red
zone of his tachometer.
You're right.
And besides,
I don't know anything
about a ring Speed's
supposed to buy for me.
The code must mean
that he's in danger.
[SPRITLE]
Mommy, I'm hungry.
Could I have something to eat?
Another midnight snack?
[MOM] Spritle, what are you
doing up at this hour?
[SPRITLE] The homing robot
came home and woke me up.
[POPS]
What?!
The robot's here!
[SPRITLE] Ice cream makes
a great midnight snack.
I'll take ice cream!
Milk is better.
[TRIXIE]
Uh-oh!
There's no note inside it!
That's not like Speed to send
it without any message in it.
[POPS]
Hmm...
But there seems to be some
red clay on the outside of it.
Oh, Spritle! What're you
and Chim Chim up to?
[TRIXIE]
Hmm...
[CLEPTO]
Ah,
what could go wrong on a
beautiful morning like this?
I can think of a million
things, Mr. Clepto.
I thought I heard a helicopter
last night. Did you hear it?
Uh-uh. I slept like
a baby last night.
Or rather, like an
old man. [chuckles]
[SPEED laughs nervously]
[SPEED]
Oh, well.
But maybe that was Trixie
searching for us last night,
and she couldn't find us.
[THUG B]
Hey! Hey, Mr. Blaggard, look!
We found one of the
natives of Misty Valley.
[BLAGGARD]
Ah, good.
We can use her as a guide
so we don't get lost.
Why do you strangers want
to go into Misty Valley?
Listen, girlie, just show us
around and don't ask questions.
I've better things to do
than to act as a guide
for the likes of you!
We'll pay ya money.
Oh! That's different! [giggles]
Oh boy, are they
greedy around here.
What do we need her for?
We can look for
the treasure alone.
This kid will tell
you the directions,
so you travel with him.
Hey! Now wait just
a minute, buster!
Ooh! I'm going
to enjoy this kid.
My name is Lana
and you're the most handsome
boy I've seen in this valley.
Someday, I'm planning
to visit the big city,
and it would be groovy if I had
a handsome boy like you
to show me around.
I'd wear a fancy dress
and comb my hair.
Will you please stop talking?
I'm tryna keep my mind
on the road up ahead.
Oh, well, the least I could do
is point out some of the points
of interest in the valley.
Oh, look! Isn't that amazing?
You mustn't miss that!
[THUG C]
Huh?
[THUG C screams]
Hey, what's the big idea?
Now's your chance to get away.
Hurry!
[SPEED]
Why are you helping us?
[giggles]
[SPEED gasps]
Trixie!
Hang on!
[growls]
[TRIXIE]
Oh, there's no one back there!
They've stopped following us.
Trixie, how in the world did
you find out where we were?
I studied the bits of red
clay on this homing robot
and figured the only place
where this clay can be found
is Misty Valley.
Pops is waiting for us
in the village up ahead.
[SPEED]
Hi, Pops.
We're safe thanks to Trixie
figuring out where we were.
Well, Pops, you might as
well call the police now.
[chuckles]
[ALL gasp]
Well, I'm glad to see
all of you again.
I've got a surprise
for you in there.
Show 'em, Tiny.
[TRIXIE]
Pops!
You can't go anywhere!
Even if you do get free,
we're keepin' the helicopter.
[gasps]
[THUG D]
Hm?
Hey, come on out!
Whoever you are!
[BOTH snicker]
[BLAGGARD]
Okay, sonny,
now you'd better take
us to the treasure.
[BLAGGARD] So you claim that
it's right around here, huh?
[SPEED]
Yes, sir.
[BLAGGARD]
What makes ya so sure?
I think the markings on the
engine stood for directions.
And according to maps,
this is where they indicated.
Hey, Boss, there's an
"X" mark back here.
[BLAGGARD]
Hm? An X?
Aah, so there is.
Okay, Tiny, move the rock aside.
[grunting]
Aah...
Just look what we
have down there.
Tiny, move it out carefully.
[ALL gasp]
Okay, open it up.
[BLAGGARD chuckles]
[CLEPTO gasps]
Take a good look at that
billion dollars, Clepto,
because that's the last
time you'll ever see it.
What do you mean?!
[BLAGGARD]
I'm getting rid of all of you.
I don't want you goin'
straight to the police.
This treasure belongs
to me and only to me.
You don't deserve a penny
of the money! Hmph!
That's what you think, girlie.
I deserve everything
I can steal.
Okay, men, they're all lined up.
Get every one of 'em!
Get ready to fire.
Ahh! It's a monkey attack!
[monkeys gibbering]
Chim Chim's the leader!
[THUGS groaning, screaming]
Who said a barrel
of monkeys was fun?!
I'll get that monkey...
Huh?!
[SPRITLE laughs]
Spritle, what are you
up to dressed like that?!
You're liable to
catch the sniffles!
[SPRITLE] Pops! Show me what
a good wrestler you are.
Good idea, Spritle.
I almost forgot I
used to be a champ.
That boss is mine!
That's the beginning.
[laughs]
[POPS yells]
Throw him, Pops!
[gasps]
[growls]
Okay... Come on! I'm ready!
Don't worry, Speed.
I'll take care of him!
[TINY growling]
[gasps]
Good work, Speed.
That takes care of him.
There aren't many more left. Ah!
Hold it right there, all of you.
One more move and
I'll pull the trigger
of this flamethrower.
[BLAGGARD laughing]
[SPEED]
Racer X!
You got here at
the right second!
[growls]
[tires screech]
[BLAGGARD]
That kid's on my tail.
I'll lay down some oil
and cause him to crash.
[screaming]
[growls]
[BLAGGARD] Now let's
see him get outta this.
The flames aren't having
any effect on that car.
I'll try water.
[chuckling]
[growls]
Send the helicopter.
I'm being chased by that kid!
Okay, come out of there!
[gasps]
[BLAGGARD]
So long!
[laughs]
[gasps]
[BLAGGARD]
Uhh... Uh!
[BLAGGARD crying]
Where's all the money
my father left me?
Where's the billion dollars?
[SPEED] It's all turned
into dust and blown away.
I'm sorry, but maybe because
the bills were buried
in volcanic ground
for so many years,
they deteriorated.
[CLEPTO]
Hmm.
Don't feel so bad, Speed.
Inspector Detector
has something to say.
First of all,
congratulations, Speed.
Gee, thanks, Inspector.
Speed, you were
instrumental in the capture
of one of the world's
most dangerous criminals.
And for that, there will
be a reward of $100,000.
[SPEED]
Oh!
Now you'll have enough money
to enter the Multi-Peak Race!
Isn't that wonderful?
Oh, Speed, we're all so proud
of you for what you've done!
[chuckles]
She's right, Speed. A great job.
Grandpa!
[CHILDREN laugh, cheer]
Now don't worry, children.
Although I didn't get the money,
we'll make out all right.
After all, who
really needs money
when they have such
wonderful children?
I'm gonna give my reward
money to Mr. Clepto.
He wants to start a home
for homeless children,
and the money's going
to be a big help.
And we'll all work hard
to earn enough money
to send you to the
Multi-Peak Race, Speed.
I'll even do some
work for a change.
[ALL laugh]
[SPEED]
Good bye, Mr. Clepto!
[TRIXIE]
Bye!
[SPEED]
Good luck!
[NARRATOR] And so,
thanks to Speed and Trixie
and Spritle and Racer X,
everything has turned out well.
But more dangerous
adventure lies ahead,
in the next thrilling
episode of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪