♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR] Speed is competing
in the Alpine Race,
the most dangerous
race in the world.
[NARRATOR] Favored to win is
the tricky Car Acrobatic Team,
consisting of seven
daredevil drivers
in cars equipped
with ingenious wings.
Their orders are to win the
trophy no matter what the cost.
[SPEED] Well, now that Pops
has redesigned the Mach 5
so that it's got small
wings underneath,
I may have a chance to beat
the Car Acrobatic Team.
Poor Pops... All that work
was too much for him.
I'm glad Trixie got
him to the hospital
and I hope he's all right.
Now we're into getting
to the higher mountains.
So far so good, but it's gonna
be really dangerous up ahead.
[SPEED] I've got the
toughest competitors
I've ever seen against me.
The Car Acrobatic Team can do
everything with their cars.
We all saw how they flew
across that deep chasm
with the river a
thousand feet below.
Not one of them crashed!
Will I be able to make it?
[SPEED]
Here ya are.
The Mach 5 driven
by Speed Racer, huh?
Well, you're running ninth.
You better pick up.
[SPEED]
I'll try.
[MAN A] You'll be hitting
bad weather ahead,
so take extra precaution.
Thanks for the warning.
[MAN A]
Get going!
[SPEED] There's something
wrong with the brakes.
[SPEED] I thought I adjusted
the brakes correctly,
but Sparky's the expert
on things like that.
If only he'd been
there to do it...
I shouldn't've argued with him.
I don't think you should
enter the Alpine Race.
I've got to, Sparky! I've got to
beat the Car Acrobatic Team.
It'll be too dangerous
even to try.
Why do you say that?
They're the best drivers
anyone's ever seen.
I know they are, Sparky! That's
why I wanna try to beat them!
I've got to prove
that I'm the best!
I've gotta accept their
challenge or give up racing.
And I'm racing no
matter what you tell me.
You are, Speed?
But they're tricky, Speed.
They'll use every dirty
trick they know to win.
Do you think I'm afraid?
Is that what you think about me?
I don't want you around
if you're not with me
a hundred percent!
[TRIXIE]
He was only trying to think
of what might be
best for you, Speed.
[SPEED]
I wish Sparky hadn't left...
Well, I hope Speed's all right,
but I know those brakes
in the Mach 5 won't last.
They've got to be changed
before the first hour of the
race is up. It's important!
If you hadn't argued with him,
you would've been there
to fix the brakes,
so now you've gotta
do it anyway!
[SPRITLE growls]
Now fix the brakes!
[SPARKY screams]
Oh. I hope Sparky's been
able to reach Speed
with the new brakes.
So did I, Trixie.
It was my fault
that Speed entered the
race with faulty brakes.
My fault... My fault...
[MOM] Pops, the doctor said
you mustn't get excited.
I'll try to catch up
to Speed by helicopter.
I've got to see him.
A helicopter might crash.
They're expecting
a storm up there.
Maybe I can get there
before the storm hits!
[MOM]
Trixie!
That's Spritle, Sparky,
and Chim Chim down there!
I was afraid something
would go wrong.
I better go down
and pick them up.
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH]
Ah, it's Trixie up there!
[SPARKY]
Hold it!
Come on, Spritle!
I'm a big boy! Don't
need help from a girl!
Come on up here, Spritle!
We've got to help Speed,
and we have very little time!
Come on, Spritle!
[SPRITLE]
You go!
Suit yourself then!
[SPRITLE]
Wait for me!
Ah! I've changed my mind!
[NARRATOR] Racer X,
whom Speed does not know
is his missing older brother.
[SPEED]
Now's my chance to pull ahead.
Oh, what's Speed doing?
We're over ice now, and he's
liable to go into a bad skid.
[SNAKE] Now we'll give
Speed a little surprise.
[gasps]
[DRIVERS screaming]
[screams]
[SPEED]
The brake doesn't work at all.
I'll try the emergency brake.
[gasping]
Calling Speed! Calling Speed!
What's your present location?!
[SPRITLE]
Where can he be?!
[SPEED]
This is Speed!
I've skidded off the
course in Skull Chasm!
My brakes have
failed completely!
[ALL gasp]
[SPARKY]
No sign of him!
Look! There's the Mach 5!
[sighs]
[SPEED screams]
Speed!
[SPARKY] Speed! Jump out!
Let the Mach 5 go!
[SPEED]
I can't!
[screams]
[SPARKY]
Jump, Speed!
[screams]
[ALL gasp]
[SPARKY]
Okay!
I'll try to grab the car!
[gasps]
[ALL scream]
[screams]
Pull it up now!
Easy!
[SPARKY]
Speed!
[TRIXIE]
Are you all right?
Pull me up... Ah...
[SPRITLE gasps]
That was a very close call!
Sparky, I'm sorry
for what I said.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have left
when you needed me.
[SPEED] Well, let's
forget about it, okay?
[SPARKY]
Okay.
Don't forget the
brakes are still bad.
Sparky, you better fix them.
I'll help you, Sparky!
[grunts, groans]
Just take it easy, Speed.
Fixing the Mach 5 is my job!
He's right, and you better use
this time for resting up, Speed.
You have a lot
more racing to do,
so go over there and sit down.
[SPEED]
Aw, Trixie, I'll be all right.
[TRIXIE]
Do as I say and rest.
Oh. We can't make Speed do
anything he doesn't want to.
Only Trixie knows
how to handle him.
But I don't want her giving
him my snack! C'mon, Chim Chim!
The radio said the other
racers are taking a break,
so why don't you have
a little lunch, Speed?
Put that back.
It's my lunch, Speed, but
I'll be glad to do without it.
Here, take it.
You're fibbing, Spritle.
You've already had yours. Now...
...go away.
Hey, somebody, please
bring me some grease!
[SPRITLE]
Okay!
[SPRITLE growls]
[chuckles]
Here ya are!
That's oil! Gimme some grease!
[TRIXIE]
This what you want, Sparky?
Yes, thanks very much, Trixie!
Too many mechanics
might spoil the car!
Let me help him!
[TRIXIE]
Keep out of the way!
[growls]
So you think I'm in the way.
Nobody talks to me like that!
Not even you, Trixie!
Put up your knuckles! Come on!
[babbling]
[TRIXIE]
Help, Speed!
[SPEED]
Huh?
[TRIXIE]
Oh!
Nobody says I'm in
the way! I'll show her!
Spritle, you'd better stop it.
Hey, what's going on?!
What's up?!
[BOTH gasp]
[TRIXIE gasps]
Speed, put me down!
What're you going to do?!
[SPEED]
Now you take a rest!
You see, Trixie, I'm not
the one in the way, you were.
[SPEED]
Okay, you're next.
[SPRITLE] Oh! Put me down!
What'd I do wrong?! Put me down!
[SPEED]
There ya are!
[TRIXIE]
You see?
[SPRITLE wailing]
Okay! The brakes are in
perfect working order!
What about you, Speed?
You haven't rested for a minute,
you've been on the
go since we got here!
Speed, you must be
pretty tired by now.
Well, the work's all done.
Let's let bygones be bygones,
and no matter how much we fight,
let's always be pals.
[SPEED]
Of course.
And we should never fight
over you racing in the Mach 5.
We won't. The Mach 5
means too much to us.
After all, our lives are
wrapped up in this car.
I'm sorry for being
such a bad boy.
Spritle, you were supposed
to be taking a rest.
Why aren't you?
I'll let you have my
friend for good luck!
But, Spritle,
isn't this supposed to
be your good luck charm?
[SPRITLE] Ah-ha. But I want
you to have it, Speed.
Just make a wish on it
and might come true!
Wish for winning the race!
All right. I'd like to win.
[SPRITLE]
Now maybe you will!
[SPEED] Hmm? I've been
sleeping too long.
I'd better hurry or I'll be late
getting back into the race.
Hmm, a storm's coming up.
[gasps]
I'm on my way, Sparky.
Say goodbye to everyone.
[SPARKY]
Be careful!
And good luck...
[SPEED] Snake, why's
the course being blocked?
I was sure you wouldn't make it.
Look.
[gasps]
With the heavy rain,
parts of the course have
been completely washed away.
It's gonna be tough.
[SPEED]
Maybe we can take another way.
[SNAKE]
There is no other way.
And when we try to get through,
we'll cause more landslides.
Besides, our tires won't take
hold in that wet ground.
We've decided to draw lots to
see which one of us goes first.
It'll be more dangerous
for each car following.
[SPEED] It's a fair way
to do it, though.
[SNAKE] Everyone that wants
to draw for being first,
step forward.
[SNAKE]
What's the matter with you guys?
Are you racing car
drivers or chickens?
All right, now come on.
What about you, Speed?
I'll draw.
[SNAKE]
Good.
Well, finally now we know
who the brave men are,
and who're the chickens.
Wait a minute.
[SNAKE]
Huh?
The masked racer, Racer X.
I'm staying in the race
and I wanna join the drawing
to see who the
first driver will be.
Be my guest, but it
won't make any difference
because I'm gonna be the
only one to get through.
Well, I'm glad
you're safe, Speed.
But you have only one life,
so you'd better be careful.
Now let's get it over with;
let's draw lots.
I have six matches. Each one
of them has marks on them.
One mark means that
driver will go first,
the other positions
will be according to
the marks on the matches.
Okay, draw.
I'll try it.
Ahh... It's got one notch
on it! That means I go first!
I go first! Wahoo!
You draw next, Tiger.
[TIGER]
Me? Uh, sure.
I'm in third place.
Next.
[BRAWN]
Two notches. I go second.
Next.
I'll be the last. You go ahead.
Heh...
[gasps]
[SPEED] Six notches.
I drew last position.
[SNAKE chuckles]
[SNAKE]
Your turn, Racer X.
I'll be in the fifth position.
It's all settled then, isn't it?
I get the fourth
position, don't I?
Start engines!
[engine revs]
[SNAKE]
Go!
Okay, Tiger, it's up
to you to make it now.
[TIGER]
Well, here goes!
Go for the Car Acrobatic Team!
I'll be following right
back of you, Tiger!
The drivers on the
Car Acrobatic Team
are supposed to be
better than that.
[SNAKE] They are.
I'll show ya. Just watch.
I'm gonna make the jump safely
and prove to you what
a fabulous driver I am.
[RACER X] Every time a
driver tries to make it,
some more of the earth caves in,
and it's going to be even worse
when we try to make the jump.
But as a professional racer,
I've got to meet the challenge.
If you're smart,
you'll give up the race.
But if you don't, good luck.
[SPEED]
Here I go...
[DRIVER A]
Don't go, kid.
There's no disgrace
if you turn back now.
[DRIVER B]
That's right, Speed.
You're just gonna throw
yourself down into the chasm
if you start now.
[RACER X]
As a professional racer,
I've got to meet the challenge.
[SPARKY] That's the worst
storm I've ever seen!
[TRIXIE]
It's a blizzard!
According to this bulletin,
not much information is
available because of the storm,
but apparently, more
than a dozen cars,
including members of the
Acrobatic Team and the Mach 5,
have had their way blocked
near Yawning Chasm Pass.
The racing committee is
considering changing the course
to a less dangerous area
before the cars and drivers
are completely wiped out.
Ohh... I hope Speed'll
be all right.
I hope he won't try to go ahead.
I'm not worried; he took my
good luck charm along with him.
It'll be just as lucky for
him as it has been for me,
right, Chim Chim?
[SPRITLE]
Please!
Say he'll be all right!
[SPRITLE wailing]
He'll bring you
plenty of good luck!
I'm gonna need it, Spritle.
[NARRATOR] Have the ice and
treacherous mountain course
been too dangerous for Speed?
And has the Mach 5 joined
the wreckage of the other cars
at the bottom of the chasm?
Is this Speed's last race?
Don't miss the next thrilling
episode of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪