♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR] The palatial mansion
of Baron Von Vondervon.
[SERVANT] Baron Von Vondervon
will now make a speech.
[BARON clears throat]
Twelve years ago, when my
daughter Yvonne Von Vondervon
was 12 years old,
she disappeared.
I will hold a Junk Car
Grand Prix in memory of her.
She always wanted to
be a racing car driver,
so the winner will get
a huge amount of money
and be treated as if
she were my own daughter.
I'll explain the rules of
the Junk Car Grand Prix.
The driver of each car
must be 17 years old.
She's allowed to, uh-- [coughs]
--have one assistant driver,
a boy or girl of any age.
Each team must build
their own car from junk.
Now, for the course.
It starts at Baron Vondervon's
palatial mountain,
crosses the spiny-peaked
mountains along Route 16,
follows Route 3 through
One Horse Town,
then the mystery road and
along Danger Pass Trail
and back here.
If any driver breaks a rule,
she will be disqualified.
The Baron realizes that
every inch of the race
is fraught with peril,
but the rewards to the winners
will make it well worthwhile.
Now, folks,
I propose a toast to tomorrow's
Junk Pile Grand Prix.
[PEOPLE chattering]
To the winner of the race,
whoever that girl may be!
[PEOPLE gasp, chatter]
Hey, what's in here?
He served us nothing
to drink but water!
I expected it.
Baron Von Vondervon is one of
the stingiest men I ever met.
I want everybody
to enjoy himself!
Maestro, play some
music for everybody!
[yelps]
[yelping]
[screams]
There's no live music.
How stingy can the Baron be?
[MAN]
Don't worry about it, Lollie.
Baron Von Vondervon's
vun-- [coughs]
--ONE of the richest
men in the world,
so when you win the race,
you'll get plenty.
And, if he keeps his word
about treating the winner
as if she were his daughter, you
might even be more than rich!
You might take over this place!
Do you really think I'll win?
[MAN]
I know it!
Hey, take a look at that
tie pin of the Baron's!
[LOLLIE]
Huh?
[gasps]
[MAN] That's a super-star topaz!
Must be worth a king's ransom!
Or at least a queen's.
Someday, it'll be yours.
That and everything else.
[laughing]
Well, Mr. Assistant Driver,
since I'm going to be
behind the wheel of the Mach 5,
we're going to win, aren't we?
You bet, Trixie.
And we'll use the money
to build an even better car.
[TRIXIE] I hope I have enough
strength to last out the race,
but I've been exercising.
I even developed a
muscle in my arm.
[gasps]
[TRIXIE]
Look, Speed,
something's the matter
with their car.
Well, that lady looks as
if she's able to fix it.
[WOMAN]
Screwdriver.
[BOY]
Here.
[WOMAN]
A spanner.
[BOY]
Here.
[gasps]
All done!
[SPEED chuckles]
[SPEED]
Uh, hiya!
Wh...? Uh-oh!
Uh, Trixie! Uh. Wait! Trixie!
Aw, don't be jealous!
Trixie, come on back!
[fireworks popping]
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Baron Von Vondervon
Junk Car Grand Prix
will start in only
a few more minutes.
[CHILD A]
We're gonna do our best to win!
I know! And maybe we will!
[CHILD B] Be careful not
to make any mistakes.
Don't worry,
you can count on me!
[CHILD B]
We will!
I didn't realize that
you and the children
would be in the race.
[WOMAN]
Oh, hi! Yes.
I decided to enter for
the sake of these children.
And she's gonna win so she
can buy us some new clothes!
And she'll be able
to take us on a trip.
And she'll be able to buy us
lots of good food to eat!
After all that, I'd better win.
We have so little
and need so much.
You see, we're from...
an orphanage.
[SPEED]
Oh, really?
Well, I sure wish you the
best of luck in the race.
--[WOMAN] Thank you.
--[TRIXIE] Speed!
Come on, you haven't
time to talk to any
pretty, young ladies right now.
Wow, look at Trixie! She's very
nervous about being in the race.
[trumpets blaring]
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen,
Baron Von Vondervon's Junk Car
Grand Prix is now underway
as the competing teams begin
putting together piles of junk
to build their cars!
[grunting]
Hurry up! Put that junk together
and stop being so lazy!
Well, where's the
steering wheel?!
And where's the speedometer?!
I've got the steering wheel!
Here it is, Mr. Freeload!
[FREELOAD]
Where's the left front tire?!
We have to have a
left front tire, too?
Go and steal a tire!
[GOON B]
Yes, sir...
[BARON]
They're working very fast.
[SERVANT]
You were very wise, Baron.
Brilliant of you to order
that all the racing cars
be made of junk.
Nobody'll lose if they crash.
[chuckles]
I wish I had my daughter back.
I miss her so much.
Everything's done.
Shall I start the car?
Okay, Trixie.
Try cranking her up!
I'm going to try the
motor now. Here goes.
[ALL cheer]
Okay, Lollie! Start up the car!
[SLIM growls]
[SLIM sighs]
[MECHANIC A] Don't worry, Slim!
We'll help you get in!
[MECHANIC B]
Heave!
[SLIM screams]
[SLIM wails]
[MECHANIC A]
I'll getcha in!
Well, we might
as well start out.
We'll use the Mach 5 to keep
an eye on Trixie and Speed.
Go, Sparky! Start her up.
[cow moos]
[screams]
What's the matter?
Is there something wrong
with the way I look?
[screaming]
[ASSISTANT]
Keep driving!
Keep it up, Trixie!
You're out in front,
and you're liable to win!
Come on, Trixie! Come on!
The way you're driving, we don't
stand a chance of winning!
Let me take over that wheel!
Trixie's still in first place!
If she keeps it up, she'll win!
Uh-oh! There's another
car about to pass us!
Now watch this, Lollie. It's the
only way we'll be able to win.
[FREELOAD]
Ah-ha!
[shrieks]
They did that on purpose!
[TRIXIE growls]
Let's go, Trixie.
You can be angry later.
There's no time now.
Well, I hope they don't
try to do that again!
A very flat tire!
Quick, get out!
[grunts]
[growls]
I'll have to put my
other plan into operation.
Calling Heliflopter No. 1,
calling Heliflopter No. 1!
[SPEED, TRIXIE gasps]
That helicopter's gonna
cause us trouble!
[GOON C] That's the car
down there. Get it!
Sure! These sleep capsules will
put 'em to sleep for a while.
Speed, I'm beginning
to feel very funny.
So am I. I wonder
what it could be...
[tires squealing]
Use the break...
[car horn blaring]
The race is going even
better than we expected.
Trixie should be reaching
the Danger Pass Trail
any minute now!
[SPRITLE]
Uh-huh!
[FREELOAD chuckles]
Sorry we have to pass you,
but I hope you sleep very well.
We must've been given
some kind of sleeper gas,
and I'll bet they're the ones...
that are behind the whole thing.
[buzzing]
[GOON E]
Heliflopter No. 2 calling.
This is Freeload.
What do you want?!
[GOON E] I spotted
another car in the lead!
Unless I do something,
it'll win! What're your orders?!
Another car in the lead?!
Go get it!
[GOON E]
Yes, sir!
Come on, you're too slow!
Step on the gas!
[LOLLIE gasps]
[FREELOAD] Quit lollygagging,
Lollie! Faster!
They almost hit us!
They'd better not try it again!
[gasps] Here they
come after us again!
[BOTH scream]
Come in, Heliflopter
No. 2, come in.
number 2, come in!
What's the matter?!
Why don't you answer me?!
Faster! Don't slow down;
step on it!
That car's stopped
in a funny place!
I'll bet something
happened to it!
Hey, look, Sparky, that's
Trixie's car, I'll bet!
Huh?! I'm afraid you're right!
[CHIM CHIM grunting]
It's all right.
Nothing happened to us.
Should we continue
with the race now?
[gasps]
It looks as if
they're coming here!
Hurry! Don't let her get away!
Take her out of that car!
[gasps]
Don't worry!
I'll fight all of 'em!
[FREELOAD]
You're coming with us!
That wasn't very nice.
Get her, men!
[FREELOAD]
Okay, men! Now you can get her!
You've caused too much trouble.
Hmm...
What're you wearing
in your hair?
A super-star topaz
worth a fortune.
I've seen one before.
This is the same kind of topaz
Baron Von Vondervon
had on his tie pin!
Where'd you get this topaz?
[WOMAN]
Give it back to me!
It belonged to my mother!
She gave it to me
before she passed away!
[FREELOAD]
Your mother?
You must be Baron Von
Vondervon's long-lost daughter
who's been missing for 12 years!
You're like money in the bank!
[LOLLIE]
Mr. Freeload! We're losing time!
Come on, hurry!
Ah, forget it! You can drive
without me from now on!
[LOLLIE]
Huh...?
[FREELOAD] I found a better way
to get my hooks into the Baron!
[laughing]
Just wait till I catch the one
who gave us the sleeper gas!
He made us lose a lot of
precious time, all right!
[TRIXIE]
Uh-huh!
Not so fast, Trixie! That car's
only made of junk, don't forget!
it's much too dangerous
to go so fast!
Don't bother me!
But this car wasn't
built to go so fast!
Well, Trixie can't say
we didn't warn her!
[SPRITLE]
Right!
Look! Something happened!
Hey! Are you all right?
Come on, wake up!
Tell me what happened!
Hey, come on!
--Wake up, wake up!
--[BOY groans]
I had a fight with some men,
but they knocked me out
and took away my friend
from the orphanage.
[SPEED]
What?!
Who were the men?!
[BOY] I don't know, but
their boss was one of the men
from the race.
I think I know who you mean.
Which way were they headed?
[BOY]
That way.
We'll look for her
after the race is over!
I'm gonna look
for her right now!
Huh?!
You're right, she's more
important than the race.
I'll continue alone!
[SPEED]
Be careful!
I hope Trixie'll be all right.
So do I. What'll we
do now, Speed?
[SPEED]
Look for that girl
and hope we're not
too late to save her.
Come on, Sparky!
Hurry!
Those men'll stop at nothing
to get what they're after!
[gasps]
[SPEED] We almost got
trapped down there!
Lucky those jacks are able
to work underwater! Hang on!
I just saw something jump out!
[GOONS screaming]
[screams]
That bazooka may come in handy!
What do you mean that
kid broke into our fort?!
Make sure he doesn't
come any further! Get him!
[GOON D]
Yes, sir!
He may have learned the secret
that you're the
Baron's daughter.
It's open! Let's go!
[GOON D]
Here they come!
[GOONS yelling]
[SPEED]
Hold it!
[FREELOAD]
Huh?
[screams]
[GOON G]
Let go of him!
Come on, let go of Mr. Freeload
or I'll open fire!
Gee, thanks, Sparky!
Let's get outta here!
I'm so grateful!
[FREELOAD groaning]
Stop them! We can't afford
to let them escape form here!
You'll never stop us!
[gasps]
[SPARKY]
They've got Trixie!
Get your filthy hands off her!
I'll let her go in exchange
for the Baron's daughter!
It's a fair exchange and
you'd better agree to it!
Hurry up! You have no more time!
Don't do what he wants, Speed!
Don't pay any attention to her!
I'm going to count to ten.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
--[SPRITLE] Huh?
--[FREELOADER] Five...
--Fire crackers!
--Six...
[SPRITLE] Thanks, Chim Chim,
you gave me an idea!
You'd better make the exchange.
It's your last chance!
Seven...
Eight!
Nine!
[screaming]
[FREELOADER]
We're being attacked!
[screaming]
That takes care of him!
[GOON G yelps]
[GOON G]
I'll get you for that!
[GOON E yells, groans]
There!
[cries]
Ah!
Why'd I start this...?
[laughs]
[gasping]
[FREELOAD yells]
I'll give her back to you
if you just let go of my arm!
[FREELOAD yelps, cries]
Maybe they'll both win,
Sparky! I hope so!
But it's impossible!
[SPRITLE]
I can hope, can I?!
[ANNOUNCER] And here they
come to the finish line...
...with Trixie in the lead!
[CROWD cheering]
[trumpets blaring]
Congratulations, Trixie,
you drove a great race.
[TRIXIE]
Thank you!
[chuckles]
And you were very brave!
[gasps]
[YVONNE] You're wearing
a super-star topaz!
[BARON]
And so are you!
Where'd you get that
super-star topaz?
[YVONNE] My mother gave it
to me just before she died.
[BARON]
Hmm...
There are only two of
these in the whole world,
and I gave the other one
to my wife years ago.
[YVONNE]
Oh!
[BARON] This proves that you're
actually my long-lost daughter.
[YVONNE]
Daddy!
[BOTH crying]
[BARON]
At last!
They think she won't have
anything more to do with them.
Yeah, and I'm afraid
she may be right.
[BARON] We'll have a big party
to celebrate the end of the race
and our reunion.
[SERVANT]
Ladies and gentlemen,
Baron Von Vondervon would
like to present to you
his long-lost daughter,
Yvonne Von Vondervon,
and here she is!
What happened to your new dress?
[YVONNE] I've decided that I'm
going back to the orphanage.
Those children are
my dearest friends
and they have nobody to look
after them the way I can.
And I wanna keep taking care
of them the way I've been doing.
I'm so happy to have
found my father,
and aren't fathers supposed
to be understanding?
So I hope you'll understand...
[BARON] I do.
You're a generous daughter.
[SERVANT]
The Baron will make a speech.
After many years of being
known as the stingiest Baron
in the world, I'm going
to give one-third--
I'm going to give one-half
of my fortune to my daughter.
And I'm going to give the
other half to the orphanage!
[YVONNE]
Oh, Daddy!
And the children may move
into my palatial mansion!
[BARON chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Speed, Trixie,
Sparky, and Spritle
leave behind a happy
group of children.
Ahead lies more adventure
in the next thrilling
episode of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪