♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR]
It began on a normal day
at one of the world's busiest
international airports.
[SPEAKER]
Flight number 603 and a half
will be landing in one minute.
The passengers will disembark
at Gate 14 and a quarter.
[THUG A]
Uh-huh.
[THUG A chuckles]
[THUG A]
Mr. Rock Force?
It's been a long time.
I don't think you remember me.
May I speak to you for a minute?
Good. It won't take very long.
This way.
[THUG A] I, uh, read in the
newspapers why you came here.
You plan to compete in
the Super Car Race, huh?
[ROCK]
That's right, I do.
But so what?
Wait a minute.
You gonna try to stop me
from racing, are you?
We sure are!
[THUGS yell, groan]
Okay... Rock!
[THUG A groans]
[helicopter whirring]
[SPEED]
There's a new race course;
it's called the Snake Track.
[TRIXIE]
Looks tricky.
Isn't that where the Super
Car Race will be held?
That's right, Trixie.
And judging by that track, it's
gonna be a tough race to win.
Teams from car factories
throughout the world
will be participating.
It looks dangerous.
It'll be tough to stay on it.
You could lose control.
[SPEED]
I know, Spritle.
There are seven curves.
And every one of them's
going to be tough;
it's gonna take all the
experience and skill
I've ever gained
to win the race!
Yeah... And it's gonna take
a tremendous amount of luck!
I can just picture those cars
leaving the track right now.
I've gotta do some practicing
on those curves
so I don't crash.
[SPARKY gasps]
[SPEED]
My timing's no good.
I've got to figure
a new technique.
A new technique,
that's what I need!
[engine revving]
Look at those clouds up there!
They're beautiful!
And it's a perfect
day for a drive.
Aw, Trixie, please stop talking.
I'm trying to figure
something out.
[TRIXIE gasps]
Oh!
What's the matter, Speed?
Why are you being
so moody today?
I don't think you've
been enjoying our drive
out to the country.
Hey!
For crying out loud, Trixie!
I asked you to be quiet!
I'm trying to think!
[TRIXIE gasps]
And you won't even tell me
what you're thinking about!
--[engine popping]
--[SPEED] Look!
[TRIXIE gasps]
Wow!
[TRIXIE]
Come on!
[gasps]
He can tip it onto two wheels!
They're trying to wreck it!
Hurry, Speed! Help him!
[yelps]
[screams]
[gasps]
[yelps]
You're all right
now, aren't you?
[ROCK]
Mm-hm.
[SPEED]
He drove the car on two wheels.
That's it! That's the
technique I've gotta use
in the Super Car Race.
Why were those men trying
to push you off the road?
Well, they could be
from a rival car factory.
But why would
they act like that?
Search me. But the whole
thing coulda been a mistake.
They might've thought
I was someone else.
[SPEED] That's a fascinating
looking automatic transmission.
I never heard of one
on a racing car before.
And I'll bet you're
a racing car driver
because of the way
you were driving.
On sharp curves, you managed
to drive on only two wheels
and you didn't lose control.
And at the same time, you
didn't slow down one bit!
You didn't downshift.
[ROCK] I can't talk to you
right now; I'm in a hurry.
[SPEED]
Hey!
[SPARKY yelps]
Okay.
I'll try it.
I'm going to try those
curves without downshifting.
But that's dangerous!
I think Speed's able to do it.
Good luck!
[SPEED]
Thanks.
Well... I hope it works.
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
[ALL scream]
Speed! You haven't been hurt!
[SPEED]
He can drive on only two wheels,
even with just one hand
on the steering wheel.
The Snake Track means nothing
to a driver like that.
Who is he, anyway?
Hey... I'll bet he's gonna
compete in the Super Car Race.
Sparky, get the Mach 5 ready.
I'm gonna drive
the curves again.
Huh?!
What're you waiting for?!
Get it ready; I've got
to practice again.
--[TRIXIE gasps]
--Oh no, Speed, better not.
You'll be hurt!
Spritle's right. It's much
too risky for you, Speed.
You heard me, get the car ready!
[SPARKY]
Oh...
[ROCK gasps]
[ROCK] Those men from the
rival car factory again!
[groans]
They'll do anything to keep me
from competing in the big race.
[knocking]
Oh, who can that be, battering
down the door at this hour?
Just a minute, I'll open it.
Couldn't you've
waited till morning?
I'm sorry, I couldn't because
I need my car fixed immediately.
Immediately?! But it's
the middle of the night!
Can't you wait till
tomorrow morning?
No, sir, please fix it now.
Tomorrow morning
could be much too late.
[POPS]
Well, where is it?
Where's you car?
[POPS]
Is that it?! T-That wreck?!
It's nothing but junk!
You must be a wild driver
to wreck it like that.
And I think it's a miracle that
you're able to stand there.
Yeah, well I wasn't driving it.
What?
Okay. How about it? Are you
going to repair my car or not?
I don't think I can.
[THUGS chuckling]
That's good to hear.
[ROCK] Look, Mr. Racer,
I'll gladly pay you anything.
I must have my car
to practice in.
Well?
[POPS]
Hm...
You're a professional
racing driver.
Well, tell me, are you going
to repair my car or not?
I already said I
couldn't, didn't I?!
I don't wanna touch it
until tomorrow morning.
[ROCK]
Oh yeah?
You're ripping my robe!
--Cut it out!
--[SPEED] Hey!
Leave him alone!
[ROCK]
Huh?!
[SPEED]
I said lea-- Oh!
Come on!
Okay...!
[BOTH grunt, groan]
Good boy! You give it to him!
Good, Speed!
[BOTH grunt, groan]
[SPRITLE]
What's going on?!
What's the big idea of
interrupting my dream?
I was dreaming about eating
a whole room full
of coconut cookies
and they were delicious.
[ROCK]
Oh, you're--!
Yes, Speed Racer's my name.
We met when you were in trouble.
I'm sorry I didn't
recognize you.
Oh, that's okay.
Friends?
Oh...
[ROCK coughs]
So you boys know each other, hm?
Pops, this man has a great
technique for sharp curves.
He drives on two wheels.
Two wheels, huh?!
[ROCK]
That's right.
Rock Force is my name.
Now will you take care
of my car, Mr. Racer?
Well, I didn't realize that
you're my son's friend.
If you agree to fix his car,
Pops, I'll be glad to help.
Thanks, Speed.
I'd be glad if you did.
I'll do it on the condition
you demonstrate to me
how you drive on two wheels.
You and your father will fix my
car only if I make a deal, huh?
Okay, you win.
Your coat is ripped
on the sleeve there.
[ROCK gasps]
[SPEED gasps]
What's the matter, Speed?
Why are you staring at me?
Well, what is it? What're
you thinking about, Speed?
What's wrong with your arm?
Mr. Force, aren't you able to
use your right hand at all?
What?
So... you've noticed, huh?
You've discovered
my secret, Speed.
I didn't suspect it.
When you were fighting Speed,
I-I never would've guessed.
And you should see how well
he drives with that arm.
The man who attacked
me the other day
is the same one who
did this to my arm.
He must be a terrible man.
In a way. But I was sort of
to blame for what happened.
I joined the Bell
Ring Race last year.
Jack Rival of the Rival
Motor Company offered me
a lot of money if I
would lose the race.
[POPS] He tried to bribe
you to lose the race, huh?
[SPRITLE] Then the
Bell Ring Race was fixed?!
[ROCK] Well, I took the
money, but I wanted to win.
So, I pulled into the lead.
And... I did win.
Fair and square, I won.
But I betrayed the
Rival Motor Company
and the man who'd
bribed me to lose.
They were waiting for me--
the whole gang of 'em.
They made sure I'd never be
able to use my right arm again.
[ROCK] I thought my
racing days were over.
How could I drive a
fast car over a track
with twists and turns in it?
I'm sorry.
What happened then?
I went to a hospital and
spent a long time there,
but the doctors couldn't help.
I can't use my arm.
Ow! Ow!
Where were the police?!
I decided if I went
to the police,
everybody would find
out about my arm
and they wouldn't
let me race again.
Mr. Force, maybe if you
exercise that right arm,
you'd get it working again.
No, I've tried exercise!
But nothing's worked.
I tried driving with
only my left arm,
but I couldn't turn the car
fast enough on the curves.
I knew that unless I had full
control over my car in a race,
I'll endanger the other
drivers as well as myself.
I have to give up my dream
of being a racing driver.
[NARRATOR]
On the other side of the city,
Jack Rival, head of
the Rival Motor company,
is holding an important
business meeting.
[RIVAL]
You incompetent stoneheads!
Can't you get rid
of a racing driver
who can't even
use his right arm?!
[THUGS]
Sorry, Mr. Rival.
Would you like us to take care
of his other arm as well?
[RIVAL]
Don't be ridiculous.
He'd tell everybody
it was no accident
and we're the one's doing it.
It would be bad for business!
I've got a special car
that'll be entered
in the Super Car Race tomorrow
and it's got to be
the winner at any cost.
That means we've
got to make sure
Rock Force is out of
the way permanently.
Any ideas how to do it?
[RIVAL]
Oh, I always have ideas.
Here. It'll be easy with this.
Easy and permanently permanent!
[ALL gasp]
And when do we do the job?
That race is tomorrow,
so get rid of him tonight!
[ROCK]
Car racing is my life.
I want more than anything to
continue being a racing driver.
It's all I care about.
But with my arm like this,
I'm not qualified to
be a racing driver!
I-I'm... just not good enough.
To qualify, I must
use my right arm.
[sobs]
Cheer up, Mr. Force.
I'm sure that your
arm will get better.
All you need is some
treatment of the proper kind,
and your arm will
be as good as new.
I don't think I'll
ever be able to use it.
Can't you invent
something for him, Pops,
so that he'll have full
control over his racing car?
It's hard. I doubt if I
can come up with anything.
You can, Pops. After all,
you built the Mach 5
and you can build any kinda
special car anyone wants.
Just give it some thought.
But even so, it would
be dangerous because
Mr. Force doesn't have
the use of his arm yet,
so he's liable to crash.
Speed's right, Spritle.
If Mr. Foce lost
control of his car,
other racers would
be in danger, too.
And we don't want anything
to happen to them.
But we've gotta do something
to help Mr. Force; I like him.
I'm glad to hear you
say that, Spritle.
You make me feel much better
and I won't forget it.
[SPEED]
Hm!
Mr. Force, I've got
an idea. Come with me.
Huh?
But it's the middle
of the night, Speed.
Where would you be going?
Just what're you
up to, Son? Well?
Please, Mr. Force,
you've got to come with me.
Hurry, there's not much time.
All right, Speed.
--[POPS] Huh?
--I'm worried.
I hope Speed'll be all right.
He's got something
up his sleeve,
but I can't imagine what it is.
Okay, Mr. Force, I want
you to drive the Mach 5.
What's the idea, Speed?
Are you trying to
make me look foolish
because I can't
use my right arm?
Please, just get in
the car and drive it.
No, I can't do it.
I can't drive it without
an automatic transmission.
[SPEED] That's not true.
You just don't wanna try.
[ROCK]
It'll just be a waste of time.
[SPEED] You're scared.
You're a coward. Get in!
I'm not a coward.
Then prove it. Drive the car.
Okay...
[engine revs]
Just what we were hoping.
He's behind the
wheel of a car again.
This time, we're gonna
get him permanently.
The only way!
Uh-oh! They're up to something.
Come on!
[SPEED]
Come on, give her some gas!
The speed limit's 80 miles
an hour through here!
You've got to go much faster!
You'll never win any races
if you drive a racing
car this slowly.
Without the use of my right arm,
I'm afraid to drive any faster.
I don't want to crash!
You're just afraid
to work the arm.
And I'm sure that
you can wake it up.
[ROCK grunts]
I can't!
Don't give up. You've gotta
use that right arm.
They're just drivin'.
They're not headed
anywhere special.
Okay, let's get
to work right now.
I'm ready.
[SPRITLE] Uh-oh! There's
going to be trouble!
[engine revving]
Open her up all the way.
Go ahead!
Hang on!
Don't be afraid!
[THUG C grumbling]
[SPRITLE, CHIM CHIM snicker]
[gasps]
[SPEED]
They're heading right toward us!
They're aiming!
--[CHIM CHIM gibbering]
--[THUG B groans]
[THUG B screams]
[THUG A yelps]
Look out!
[ROCK gasps]
[BOTH grunting]
[THUGS screaming]
[SPRITLE]
Speed!
What's going on?
Those men were trying
to get Mr. Force.
And they would have if
I hadn't stopped them.
Thank you, Spritle.
You saved my life.
You sure did, Spritle.
A fine job!
Now listen to me.
Mr. Force, I think you should
enter the big race tomorrow.
You have a very good
chance to win it.
[ROCK]
What?
You're kidding!
[SPEED] I don't kid about
things like that. I mean it!
According to the rules,
a racer must be in tip-top
shape to compete in the race.
And you can drive
as well as any man
who has full use of both arms,
even better than some!
Speed's right. You're one of
the best drivers I've ever seen.
[ROCK]
Hm.
Let's face it.
In tomorrow's race,
you and I are gonna be
competing against each other,
and it's gonna
be a tough fight.
Right.
And I'll beat you, Speed.
[SPEED]
We'll see about that.
Anyway, good luck.
[ROCK]
Good luck to you.
[DRIVER A groans]
What a race... [groans]
Go, Speed! Come on!
--You can win!
--[SPRITLE] Wow!
Speed's pulling ahead.
Nobody can beat
him now, I'll bet.
Don't be so sure.
Mr. Force is going faster;
he's catching up to him!
I'm worried about
those sharp curves.
[SPEED grunts]
Watch out, Speed! Hurry up!
--Get rid of him!
--Go!
This is your last
chance to pull ahead!
[ROCK]
He passed me.
I've got to overtake him.
[SPEED]
I'm in the lead.
But if I don't keep it now,
I'll lose the race.
--Come on, Speed! Come on!
--[SPRITLE] Go!
[SPEED grunts]
[ALL]
Go!
Pass him!
Come on, pass him!
Faster!
[ANNOUNCER]
Rock Force wins!
Both racers crossed the finish
line at almost the same instant,
but Rock Force wins the trophy!
That was amazing!
How's it feel to be
the winner of the race?
Please come to the judge's
stand for your award.
Wait a minute, you can't
give him the trophy.
He's disqualified; he has
the use of only one arm.
Huh?!
Just what do you mean?
[THUG A] Without the use of his
right arm, he's disqualified.
He doesn't deserve
to win the trophy.
Listen, I won the race
fair and square.
[THUG C]
Let go of him!
[yells]
[THUG A groans]
[laughing]
Aw, what's the use of
fighting? You lost anyway.
On your feet!
--[THUG A] Okay.
--Now cut it out.
There's to be no fighting. Stop!
[THUG A] Get your hands
off me; let me go!
[SPEED]
Hold it.
Don't hit him again.
[gasps]
Huh?!
I used my arm! I used my
right arm to hit him with!
[SPEED] That means there's
nothing wrong with it!
My right arm is
completely well again!
You gentlemen lied
to me about his arm!
[THUGS laugh nervously]
Congratulations!
Congratulations, Mr. Force!
And I'm sorry you
didn't win, Speed.
But we know you did your best.
Speed, thank you.
You helped me a lot.
I'll win the next race
that we're in together.
Will you? I'll win it!
[SPEED gasps]
[NARRATOR] Be sure to see the
next exciting episode of...
...Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪