♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[SPEED] The Kingdom of
Saccarin had asked Pops
to build a mini-racing car.
And now it was
finished and we were
putting the last touches
of polish on it,
getting it ready for
the Baby Grand Prix
to be held in celebration of
the coronation of Prince Jam.
This mini-racer is
the finest ever built.
[POPS] I'll bet
Prince Jam's going to be
very pleased with this car.
Pops, you worked
hard building it.
Aren't you sorry you
have to give it away
to the Prince of Saccarin?
Yes, but it was at his country's
request that I build it
when they came to me as
an expert on racing cars.
It was a real honor!
And because I built the Mach 5,
I guess I'm
becoming world famous.
--[laughs]
--[SPRITLE] Hey, Pops!
I wanna race in the Grand Prix.
Make one for me.
You're too young yet.
[SPRITLE]
Aw...
Spritle, how many times
do I have to tell you.
The race is for
eight to 13 year-olds.
You're seven years,
11 months and 23 days, and--
and eight hours old,
to be exact!
That's pretty close, so why
can't we lie a little about it?
We're not going to lie about it!
[SPRITLE]
Gee, Pops, it's not fair!
[POPS]
Huh?! What's not?
Giving a fabulous car
like this to a boy
in a country nobody heard of.
Ahh!
[SPRITLE gasps]
I told you to keep your
hands off; get away!
[SPRITLE gasps]
Until we give this
car to Prince Jam,
I don't want... it scratched...!
Let's make a deal.
If you won't build me a car,
take me to Saccarin with you.
I wanna see what kind of
race track they have there.
Sorry, Spritle, but we can't.
When we deliver the
car to the Prince,
we'll be carrying
so much luggage that
there won't be any room for you.
You'll have to stay home,
and that's final.
[SPEED]
But don't feel badly, Spritle.
I'll bring you back
a lot of souvenirs.
[SPRITLE] Hmph! You're
beginning to sound like Pops.
Gee, Pops, it's too bad
there isn't room for him.
There's nothing we can do.
I don't care what they say;
we're going to Saccarin!
We just have to find a way.
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[screams]
Afternoon!
[flute plays]
[BOTH yelp]
[KING] Aah, Mr. Pops Racer
and his retinue. You may rise.
Welcome, Mr. Racer,
to my country.
Thank you, Your Majesty,
we've come to deliver
the mini-racing car you
ordered custom-built
for the Baby Grand Prix.
[KING]
Aah!
[POPS] Would Your Highness
kindly inspect it?
[TRIXIE giggles]
Pops sounds so formal;
he sounds ridiculous!
[SPEED]
Quiet, Trixie!
A masterpiece of automotive art.
Hm.
Prince Jam will be thrilled
to have such a marvelous car.
Thank you, Your Royal
Highness Majesty,
for your flattering words.
Please don't stop.
The Prince hasn't
said anything yet.
[KING] Oh, did you think
this is Prince Jam?
No, no, no. This is his
cousin, Prince Sugarin.
Prince Jam is somewhere
in town right now,
but he'll be back later.
Your Majesty, we brought
the car for Prince Jam
and brought you a personal gift.
Did you? That's very thoughtful.
Give it to me right now.
[POPS]
Coming right up!
Hm, the gift isn't here.
The case is missing! It's gone!
It must've fallen out of the
car somewhere along the way.
[POPS]
What're we going to do?!
[SPEED]
Trixie and I'll go look for it.
[POPS]
Good.
Come right in and try the
specialty of the house--
curried rice,
chocolate tadpoles,
and gingered grasshoppers,
one of the most native dishes
guaranteed to satisfy
even the most
discriminating of appetites.
And I promise,
it will fill you up.
Once you start,
you won't want to stop.
Try it!
Looks delicious! Maybe it's
not as bad as it sounds.
I'm starving, Chim Chim,
and so are you,
so why don't we just dig in
and see if we like it?
I don't have any idea where
we could've dropped it.
Speed, it's possible
that someone
came along and picked it up.
[SPEED]
I suppose so.
The poor King.
He's disappointed.
Where could it be?
--[TRIXIE] Speed!
--[SPEED] Huh?
That looks like
the case over there,
under that canopy!
[SPEED]
You're right! That's it!
[TRIXIE] Open it. See if
the gift's still there.
The King's gift is gone!
I wonder what happened to it!
[COOK]
What's the big idea?!
[SPRITLE groans]
You said to try it!
We did and we liked it,
but we don't have any money!
[COOK]
I didn't say it was free!
You had better report those
two moochers to the police.
I recognize them!
They stowed aboard again!
Run, Chim Chim!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[COOK]
Thieves! You've got to pay!
[SPEED]
Spritle, come back here!
[SPRITLE, CHIM CHIM grunt]
[COOK yelps]
[COOK] Ugh! I want my
money and I'll get it!
[COOK groans]
[SPEED]
Uh-oh!
Trixie, pay him
whatever the food costs
and tell Pops what's happened
while I try to catch
Spritle and Chim Chim!
I'll see you later.
[SPRITLE gasps]
How am I ever gonna find Spritle
in this tremendous crowd?
Who's the boy on the elephant?
That's His Highness, Prince Jam.
Prince Jam... Hm.
He's the one who's
going to get
the mini-racing car Pops built.
[VILLAIN A]
Ready?
[VILLAIN B]
Ready.
[VILLAIN C]
Ready!
[VILLAIN A]
Good.
Now!
[VILLAIN A]
One!
[VILLAIN B]
Two!
[VILLAIN C]
Three!
[PEOPLE screaming, coughing]
This parade's ridiculous.
[SPEED]
Spritle!
[SPRITLE gasps]
Now come with me!
Run, Chim Chim!
Spritle, come back
here! Come back!
Spritle! Chim Chim!
[PRINCE JAM] You let me go!
I'm His Royal Highness!
You can't do this to me! [cries]
[VILLAIN A] Hold still.
Nobody's going to hurt you!
[VILLAIN B]
Are you ready?
[VILLAIN C]
Ready!
[PRINCE JAM]
Unhand me!
[VILLAIN A] You stoneheads!
What are you doing to me?!
Catch the Prince!
[PRINCE JAM gasps]
[VILLAINS groan]
[VILLAIN A]
He's getting away!
[MAN A yelps]
[MAN B screams]
[VILLAINS grunt]
--[VILLAIN A] Faster!
--[VILLAIN B] Faster!
[VILLAIN C]
Faster!
[SPRITLE, CHIM CHIM gasp]
[SPRITLE]
Run!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[MAN C]
Hm?
Spritle, wait!
Spritle!
[SPRITLE]
Hurry, Chim Chim!
[PRINCE JAM]
Oh!
[panting]
[BOTH groan]
[VILLAIN A, B]
There he is!
[VILLAIN C]
Get him!
[screams]
Hey, what are you doing
to that boy over there?
[VILLAIN A]
He's nosy! Let's get him. Ready?
[VILLAIN B, C]
Ready!
[VILLAINS grunting]
[SPEED gasps]
[grunts]
[SPEED, VILLAIN A grunt]
[screams]
[GUARD A]
Look! There's the Prince!
[GUARDS chattering]
[GUARD B]
Well, is he all right?
[GUARD C]
H-He's asleep!
[GUARD A]
Everyone, stand back!
Your Majesty, come on.
Let's go back to the palace.
[VILLAINS yelping]
[VILLAIN A]
Retreat!
They were terrific fighters.
I don't see Spritle any place.
I wonder where he went.
[gasps]
Spritle, you can't fool me by
dressing up to look
like the Prince!
You deserve a good spanking
and you're going to get it!
Unhand me, you knave!
Oh, no! Now you're even trying
to sound like the Prince.
But it won't work. Let's go.
[PRINCE JAM gasps]
Put me down!
[GUARD A gasps]
No monkeys allowed
in the royal car!
[VILLAIN A grunts]
[VILLAIN A]
One!
[VILLAIN B]
Two!
[VILLAIN C]
Three!
Stoneheads! Pumpkin noggins!
How can you come back
here without him?!
[VILLAIN A]
Sorry, Omar Offendem.
[OFFENDEM]
Sorry?!
How can we take over the country
if you apologize all the time?!
[VILLAIN B] We'll see that
Prince Sugarin gets crowned.
Not so loud!
Nobody knows that
we are scheming to
put Prince Sugarin
on the throne.
He'll do whatever
we tell him to do.
And by using him
as our figurehead,
we'll control all of Sacarrin!
[VILLAIN A]
We did our best
to get rid of
Prince Jam, didn't we?
Your best wasn't good enough;
you failed to do the job!
[VILLAIN C]
I'm sorry, Offendem!
[OFFENDEM]
Get back!
It's disgusting.
Prince Jam's as well as if
nothing happened to him.
[SPRITLE]
They think I'm Prince Jam,
so all I have to do
is act like Prince Jam!
And then I'll get to
drive Pops' mini-racer!
And I'll wearing fancy
clothes and eat forever.
This is a life fit for a king!
[SPRITLE gasps]
[laughs]
[STAFF A]
Monkeys are not allowed!
[SPRITLE groans]
I hope the plan is clear.
We must grab Prince Jam
and get him out of the way
before the coronation,
so that the crown
will be put on
Prince Sugarin's head!
All right, come down here!
--[VILLAIN A] One!
--[VILLAIN B] Two!
[VILLAIN C]
Three!
[OFFENDEM] Tonight,
put this in Prince Jam's
new mini-racing car.
[VILLAINS]
Hmm?
[OFFENDEM]
It's a remote control device
that will operate remotely.
The Baby Grand Prix
may be our last chance
to get Prince Jam,
so you better not fail!
[VILLAIN A]
We won't fail, Offendem!
Remember, tomorrow's big race
will be our big opportunity!
[OFFENDEM cackles]
[POPS] That's right, sir.
Spritle is right here.
And as soon as the race
is over, we'll head for home.
[PRINCE JAM] Open up or I'll
call the Royal Guards!
You can't lock royalty up like
this; it's against the law!
Let me out! Let me out!
I command you, open the door!
Open it up! Hey!
He's still trying to
pretend he's the Prince.
I didn't realize how badly
Spritle wanted to
drive the mini-racer.
I feel sorry for him,
but maybe he'll calm down
and get over it if we
keep him locked up.
[PRINCE JAM]
Open this door!
It's time for us to go.
After all, the race'll
be starting soon.
[PRINCE JAM]
The Baby Grand Prix?
I've got to be in the race!
[grunting]
If you don't let me out,
I'll have you put in jail!
You'll be locked up forever!
He needs to be punished.
And just for that, he can
stay locked up in there
until the race is over.
Maybe it'll teach him a lesson
he won't forget in such a hurry.
[PRINCE JAM] Open this door
or you'll be sorry!
Open up! Open this door!
[PRINCE JAM groans]
[water trickling]
[PRINCE JAM]
Hm?
Ah! I got it!
[snickers]
[POPS] I assure you, Your Royal
Imperial Majestic Highness,
the car's in tip-top
royal condition.
It's fit for a king to drive,
even a future king.
Thank you, everybody.
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[SPEED]
What's he trying to tell us?
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[ANNOUNCER] At last, the
Baby Grand Prix of Saccarin
is about to get underway
in celebration of the
coronation of Prince Jam!
Young racers between
the ages of eight and 13
from all over the world
will be competing.
Even though the cars
are smaller than
the standard racing cars,
they have tremendous power
and it'll be an exciting race!
Help! Let me out of here! Help!
[PRINCE JAM]
Open the door!
[STAFF B]
Right away!
[screams]
[trumpets playing]
All mini-racers are
now in position,
and the race is about to start!
[engines rev]
[PRINCE JAM panting]
[PRINCE JAM]
Wait for me! I'm not ready yet!
[engines revving]
[PRINCE JAM]
Hurry! Get out of the way!
You're going to make me
late for the race! Hurry!
[ANNOUNCER]
Three minutes!
[PRINCE JAM panting]
[PRINCE JAM]
Don't start! I command you!
Don't start without me!
[ANNOUNCER]
Two minutes!
[PRINCE JAM]
Let me through! I'm Prince Jam!
[WOMAN]
Hey!
Ten seconds more!
[PRINCE JAM]
Don't start yet!
[PRINCE JAM gasps]
[MAN D]
Keep back, sonny.
That sure is a wonderful
car you built, Pops.
[OFFENDEM snickers]
In the 15th lap, Prince Jam's
car is still leading!
[SPRITLE] This is fun, and they
still think I'm Prince Jam.
Ahh!
[VILLAIN A snickers]
[SPRITLE gasps]
[CROWD gasps]
There's something wrong with the
steering on Prince Jam's car!
[POPS]
That's impossible.
My steering systems always work!
[SPEED]
It's not working now!
He might even have trouble
coming into the pit
for a check-up.
I'll help.
Oh, no!
[SPRITLE screams]
[SPRITLE]
The brakes don't work!
The steering doesn't
work either!
What am I going to do?!
[engine revs]
[SPRITLE]
Don't your brakes work either?!
They're fine!
Only yours don't work!
[screams]
[VILLAIN C snickers]
[SPRITLE gasps]
That mask was too
hot on my face!
Hey, wait a minute! Did you
do something to my car?
Yeah, Prince Jam! We
really fixed up that car!
Prince Jam?
You've made a terrible mistake.
I'm not the Prince!
I'm only Spritle!
[SPEED] I hope that car
and the Prince are all right!
We're coming to the
best place up ahead!
Get ready to get rid of the
Prince once and for all!
[SPRITLE gasps]
Hey... H...
Ahh!
[groans]
[VILLAIN A snickers]
[tires screech]
[gasps]
[screams]
Help me, Speed!
[SPEED]
Hang on!
[NARRATOR] Is this the end of
the road for Spritle and Speed?
Don't miss the next thrilling
episode of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪