♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[SPEED]
The statue of Isis!
And I've got to bring it
back within one hour!
[SPEED gasps]
[SPEED] The story really
began when Calcia,
daughter of famous
archeologist Dr. Bone,
discovered the ruins
of Cleopatra's palace.
And Trixie and I went
searching for Calcia,
who had disappeared.
A falling rock had
struck her on the head.
And she now believed
that she was Cleopatra.
Splint Femur,
Dr. Bones' assistant,
was also along
on the expedition.
And now he planned
to use Cleopatra--
Or rather, Calcia, to
command the local men
to dig for Cleopatra's treasure.
Trixie and I were captured
by the evil Femur,
who threatened that unless
I drove to a distant pyramid,
retrieve the statue of Isis
atop it, and returned--
all within two hours,
before a shadow reached
the eye of the Sphynx--
Trixie would have
to pay with her life.
[gunshots]
[SPEED gasps]
[SPEED grunts]
[THUGS gasp, whimper]
[screams]
[SPEED panting]
[yelps]
[SPEED]
There it is!
[TRIXIE]
Oh, Speed. You've got to hurry!
The shadow has almost
reached the statue's eye.
[THUGS chuckling]
[THUG A grunting]
[FEMUR]
Slaves! Look at this girl!
Let her be your example!
Whoever turns against Cleopatra
will suffer the same fate!
[SPEED grunts]
There's no time left!
[SPEED]
I'll use the homing robot
to get the statue back to them.
[SPEED]
I hope it gets there in time.
[TRIXIE gasps]
The time is up!
Lower her into the fire.
Stop lowering her!
The sun is behind the clouds.
Wait till it comes out.
No, the time is up and we
cannot show her any mercy.
Lower her away!
[CALCIA] No! I command
you to wait for the sun!
The shadow reached
the eye. Lower her!
You must not burn her.
[TRIXIE sighs]
That's the statue, but
the young man has failed
to return in person, and
that was part of the bargain,
if you remember.
He himself was to
bring the statue back,
otherwise, the girl
would pay with her life.
He's failed to return,
so she must pay!
You are right, Femur,
so do as you want.
[tires screech]
[gasps]
--[SPEED grunting]
--[THUGS groaning]
[yells]
[groans]
[SPEED grunts]
[THUG B]
Stop him!
--[SLAVES murmuring]
--[SPEED] Wait!
[FEMUR]
Huh?!
Speed!
[SPEED]
Hold it!
You're rude in the
presence of Her Majesty.
Take him away! Get rid of
him as well as the girl!
Wait! Although he failed
to return in time,
he did manage to deliver
the statue in time.
And therefore, both of
their lives shall be spared.
But from now on, they must
join the rest of my slaves
who are trying to
dig up the treasure.
[clanking]
We can't complain, Trixie.
After all, we're still alive.
But they give us hardly any
food and the work is very hard,
so we won't be able to last
much longer, I'm afraid.
I've gotta figure some way
for both of us to escape.
[TRIXIE]
But even if we did get away,
we're still in the
middle of the desert!
We'd be all right if we
could get into the Mach 5.
Stop talking and
get back to work!
[SPRITLE]
All hail the Queen!
[BOTH]
That's Spritle's voice!
[FEMUR] Where shall we
dig next, Your Highness?
The best place to try to
find my hidden treasure
is over at the bottom
of that hill,
near the ceremonial
house built by my father,
Patrameus the 13th.
[FEMUR] We shall do as
you say, Your Highness.
Ever since she was hit
by that falling rock,
I've got to humor her.
What was that you said, Femur?
[FEMUR]
Uh, nothing, Your Highness!
[SPRITLE]
Bow down to the ground, Slaves.
All hail Cleopatra!
All hail the Queen!
[TRIXIE] That wasn't
very nice of Spritle!
[SPRITLE, CHIM CHIM chuckle]
[snoring]
[elephant trumpets]
[SPEED]
Huh?
Come on, Trixie, come on!
--Wake up!
--[TRIXIE] Huh?
[SPEED grunts]
[TRIXIE grunts]
[SPRITLE]
Come on!
The Mach 5's nowhere in sight!
They must've taken it away.
It's in the warehouse.
[SPEED] Oh no! How'll
we ever get in there?
[SPRITLE]
Don't worry.
I think I know where I could
find a key to that warehouse.
I'll go get it.
[TRIXIE]
Okay. Good luck!
[FEMUR snoring]
[SPRITLE, CHIM CHIM gasp]
[FEMUR] Mm... Treasure...
Mountains of treasure...
[SPRITLE gasps]
[CHIM CHIM humming]
[FEMUR]
Huh?
[SPRITLE]
Mm-hm!
[THUGS groaning]
Your Majesty,
I must talk to you.
[CALCIA]
Go ahead.
[TRIXIE]
The other day, my friend Speed
was competing in the Sahara Race
when he met your father,
the famous archeologist.
[CALCIA scoffs]
That's ridiculous.
My father was Patrameus the 13th
and he hasn't been
with us for 13 years.
[TRIXIE] Hm?! I don't
mean Cleopatra's father!
I mean your real one,
Dr. Digger Bone.
Dr. Bone! I've heard that name
somewhere before, but where?
It rings a bell.
[TRIXIE] Maybe this will
bring Calcia's memory back!
[TRIXIE]
Please come with me!
[SPEED] Well? Any luck?
Did you get the key?
Sure, Speed. Here it is! Catch!
Great work, Spritle!
[THUG C]
What was that?!
[SPEED]
The Mach 5!
And over there is some of
the real Cleopatra's treasure
that they must've
dug up already.
Someone's coming. Let's hide.
[THUG C] Look! The door's
open. Check into it!
[THUGS]
Yes, sir!
[THUGS groaning]
[THUG D groans]
[SPEED]
Spritle! Hurry, come on!
Wow! He's my brother
and he sure can fight!
I wonder where Trixie is.
What's taking her so long?
[SPEED]
I hope she's all right.
There she is! Trixie, hurry!
Come on, Trixie!
Time's wasting; hurry!
[TRIXIE]
Coming!
[engine sputtering]
[TRIXIE]
What's the matter, Speed?
Why aren't we going?
[SPEED]
There's no gas!
You mean we're stuck?
[SPEED]
Right.
[FEMUR cackling]
Your Majesty!
They are not your friends!
They were trying to take
you away from your country!
Then you ought to punish them!
[THUG E] Now you won't be
able to try anything else.
You will never again
bother Her Majesty.
We're going to see to that.
--[TRIXIE] Oh, Speed!
--[SPRITLE] Speed!
And as for the rest of you,
you can go back to work
as slaves digging for
the rest of the treasure.
Tell me, Femur. What're
you planning to do to me?
I've planned an interesting
way to get rid of you.
We filled your gas tank
and we're going to run
your car and you right
into the Nile River.
Have a good swim in the Nile!
Oh, no!
[SPRITLE gasps]
Poor Speed!
[gasps]
[laughs]
That finishes him for good.
We'll never hear from him again.
[laughing continues]
[SPEED grunting]
[THUG F]
You! Get back to work!
All right! Don't shoot again!
[whimpers] We haven't
eaten since yesterday!
You promised to take good
care of us if we worked hard,
but you haven't
given us anything!
[THUG F]
We promised to take care of you?
All we promised was that
you'd have to work hard.
And you'd better
do that or else!
I've never met anyone so cruel!
[THUG G]
Work! Work!
Somehow, I feel that Speed'll be
all right and he'll rescue us.
Oh, Spritle! That would
be too good to be true.
--[SPRITLE growls]
--[THUG H] Huh? Hm?
--[burps]
--Hah?!
[THUG H]
Huh?!
--[screams]
--[THUG H screams]
[ALL laugh, cheer]
There's not much
fun in being slaves,
so open this gate
and let us out!
He's got an itchy
trigger finger,
so you better do as he says.
Hold that itchy
trigger finger still.
I'll open the gate.
I just don't think you
slaves are playing fair.
[SLAVE A]
Come on!
[FEMUR cackles]
[ALL gasp]
[FEMUR cackling]
You'll never get away.
Go back to your cell,
while you still can.
We're surrounded!
We haven't a chance!
[FEMUR]
So you refuse to go back, eh?
Good! Then we can
get rid of you.
Fire!
[THUGS groan]
The police!
You're finished, Femur!
You'd better throw down
your guns and surrender!
Oh! It's Speed and he's alive!
He's come to rescue us!
[SPEED]
Femur! Look around you.
Look at all the
police I've brought.
You have no choice
but to give up.
[FEMUR chuckles] You are in
the Palace of Patrameus.
No one is allowed in here,
not even the police!
You have angered our stone gods.
For that, you'll have to pay.
They will punish you, not
only for what you have done,
but as an example to any
other nosy strangers.
--[SLAVES gasp, murmur]
--Don't be afraid!
Speed and the police will
bring that man to justice;
I'm sure of that.
--[rumbling]
--[SPEED gasps]
[ALL scream]
[screaming continues]
[CALCIA screams]
[groans]
[BOTH scream]
[TRIXIE groans]
Trixie!
Trixie! I'll fight it!
You go and see if
you can help Calcia!
Calcia! Where are you, Calcia?
Calcia!
[THUGS groan]
[ALL gasp]
[SPEED groans]
[SPEED]
Femur!
He's trying to get away!
[SPEED groans]
Hurry! We've got to get
the treasure out of here!
[TRIXIE]
Speed!
[SPRITLE]
Speed! Speed!
--[SPRITLE] Speed! Speed!
--[CHIM CHIM gibbering]
[SPRITLE]
They're getting away!
What?! Femur's getting away?!
--[SPRITLE] Yes!
--I'll go after him!
[SPEED grunts, gasps]
[FEMUR chuckles]
Farewell, land of the Pharaohs!
Continue to sleep as
you have for centuries.
Sleep forever for all I care
because I've got
more your treasures
than I'll be able to squander
in a lifetime of high living.
What's this?
My co-pilot's a traitor?
No, Femur, you betrayed me.
We both came here
as archeologists
on an expedition to find the
lost treasures of Cleopatra.
What's happened to you?
You no longer think
you're Cleopatra!
If it hadn't been for you,
my father would still be alive!
And you used me to get
Cleopatra's treasure
for your own selfish uses.
Because of you, the people here
were forced to work as slaves!
You won't stop me from carrying
out the rest of my plan.
[CALCIA gasps]
You served my purposes, Calcia,
but now you're in my way.
I don't need you any longer.
First, let me thank you for
imagining you were Cleopatra
after that stone hit your head.
You were a great help to me.
[FEMUR chuckles]
Goodbye, Calcia.
[FEMUR gasps, groans]
[FEMUR]
Now! Kid!
[BOTH grunt, groan]
[CALCIA screams]
[FEMUR groans]
[SPEED]
We've got to bail out!
Jump out! Quick!
Calcia, this pendant is yours.
I came across it and
matched it to your picture.
That's how I was
able to find you.
[CALCIA]
Oh, thank you, Speed.
[NARRATOR] Be sure to see the
next thrilling episode of...
... Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪