♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR]
These are the Saline Flats,
testing grounds for the
fastest land vehicles on Earth.
Here, through the use of
the latest electronic equipment
which times the
velocity of the vehicle
to the fraction of a second,
old speed records
are often broken.
But so are many hearts and
hopes when disaster strikes.
Today, a new car,
a supersonic rocket car
designed by Pops Racer,
is to be tested
for the Vavoom Motor Company.
This car is expected to
smash all known speed records
and open possibilities for
transcontinental land travel
comparable to that
of our fastest jet planes.
Every facet of this
revolutionary new design
has been robot control tested.
But today comes the ultimate
test with a human driver.
Selected for this
important testing assignment
is one the youngest
but most skillful
and successful racing
drivers in the world,
none other than Speed Racer.
Twenty seconds before ignition.
[POPS]
Fifteen seconds...
[SPEED]
Fuel injector lever is set.
[POPS]
Ten seconds...
5... 4... 3...
[POPS]
...2... 1...
Start!
[SPARKY]
Mach 0.3!
0.4!
0.5!
[ALL gasp]
[SPARKY]
Mach 1!
[NARRATOR]
The main office building of
the Vavoom Motor Company.
The Vavoom Motor Company
put all its efforts and money
in the supersonic car.
We hoped to establish
a new speed record
and challenge the entire
automotive industry.
But we failed.
[FERNO] Mr. President,
I think something's wrong
with the design.
Yes, it's my personal opinion
that bad crashes like that
are caused by bad design.
Now, Pops Racer has always
been an excellent designer,
but he could have
made a critical blunder.
Or the driver of the
supersonic car made the error.
There were no mistakes.
Wait a minute, gentlemen.
An investigation
is being conducted.
Let's wait for the results
before we try to fix the blame
for what happened
to our supersonic car.
[ENGINEERS muttering]
Hey, Chief, come over here
and look at this.
[CHIEF]
Coming!
Well? Did you find something?
Here, sir.
Someone broke this
screw right in half.
[CHIEF]
Hmm?
A special screw like that
doesn't break under pressure.
I think it was
sabotaged by someone--
Shh!
Well, nobody can
hear us in the car
and I've got to
tell you my theory.
[BLACKET chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
[BLACKET] Even the walls
on cars have ears.
I'll tell you
what you're gonna tell
the President
of Vavoom Motor Cars.
[knocking]
Ah, Chief, you're here.
We've been anxious to hear the
results of your investigation.
Who's that with you?
He's my-- My...
...my assistant.
All right, go ahead.
Tell us about the investigation.
--[CHIEF] Well, I--
--[BLACKET] Go ahead.
Did you find out what made
the supersonic car crash?
Not exactly, but we
made a careful check
and every part of
the car was perfect.
Nothing mechanical had failed.
Apparently, the accident
was caused by, uh...
[BLACKET]
Make it sound good.
Well, I don't want to put
the blame on any one person,
but it seems apparent.
I understand.
You're trying to say that
the car was badly designed.
Mr. Racer was
responsible for that.
Either he's the one to blame...
...or Speed did
a bad job driving.
[SPEED]
Huh?!
I'll be the one to decide
who's responsible for the crash.
In the meantime,
another model of the
supersonic car must be built.
Huh?! Build another model?!
Right, we'll keep on
building supersonic cars
till we break the speed record.
And we'll follow Pops'
design for the car again.
[BUSINESSMAN A]
Oh no, not the same design.
[BUSINESSMEN murmuring]
[PRESIDENT]
Quiet, Gentlemen!
Don't you remember?
You once told me you considered
Pops' design
for the car the best.
So we'll use it.
But instead of Speed, we'll
hire a different test driver.
Let's start looking
for a new driver.
[SPEED]
They're wrong.
I was not to blame
for that crash.
But what could have caused it?
I was going so fast and
it all happened so quickly.
Any one of a thousand things
could've gone wrong.
Mr. Racer's been a top designer,
but he could have
made a bad blunder.
Or the driver
made the bad mistake.
I blame Speed Racer
for the crash.
Could Mr. Ferno be right?
Is the car too powerful
for me to handle?
Could I have caused it to crash?
Am I finished as
a racing car driver forever?
[BUSINESSMAN B] Gentlemen,
please. Give me your attention.
Applicants for
test driving, get in line.
You'll just have
to wait your turn.
The car already crashed once,
but those men are ready
to risk their necks.
The Vavoom Motor Car Company
must be stopped,
you've got to
do something, Blacket.
Don't worry, Mr. Tycootis.
Just leave it to me.
[chuckles]
[TYCOOTIS] Isn't that Speed
Racer's car, the Mach 5?
[BLACKET]
Yeah...
[TYCOOTIS]
The poor kid.
He's fired but he won't give up!
[TYCOOTIS chuckles]
All applicants step
forward one-by-one
and give me your names.
All right, what's your name?
Pete Pistonock, sir.
This is your number
for the test.
What's your name?
[screams]
Wait a minute, we only
want racing drivers here,
not monkeys.
And not children either.
And not girls either!
You're wasting my time,
so the three of you
might as well go on home.
Not so fast, Mister.
We're not here to try out
for the job of test driver.
Go ahead, Speed.
Apply for the job.
Come on, next.
Speak up, what's your name?
But Trixie, they already
fired me from the job.
The supersonic car's
crash wasn't your fault
or the fault of
Pops' design either!
It's just a mystery, that's all.
Maybe a spy from another company
put something in the car
to make it crash.
No, Spritle.
I guess I'm to blame.
No one else.
Speed... You're a great driver;
you mustn't give up.
Thanks, but you're beginning
to sound just like my father.
[SPRITLE]
Come on, Speed!
Don't be scared.
Come on, try out for the job.
Okay, Spritle, you win.
First question:
What is the world record
for automobile speed?
It's held by an American car.
In 1964, the American
Dream number 3
won at 500.5 miles an hour.
Very good.
Next applicant, please.
Mm-mmm. I'm sorry, but you're
not what we're looking for.
Next applicant is number 555.
[ALL gasp]
[PRESIDENT]
Put him through the tests.
His reactions are sharp.
His nerves are perfect
for test driving the car.
[BUSINESSMAN C] Uh, Mr.
President, we have the results
of all the applicants' tests.
[PRESIDENT]
Good, and what are the ratings?
Which one of them is at
the top of the list?
[BUSINESSMAN C] This one, sir.
Number 555, Speed Racer.
[PRESIDENT]
Hmm...
[FERNO]
But, sir!
His name should be
taken off the list.
He smashed up the car once and
if he gets behind the wheel,
he's liable to do it again.
Mr. Tycootis? This is
Dante Ferno calling you back.
[TYCOOTIS]
Mm-hmm.
I heard about Speed being hired.
But don't worry about it.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, I made some plans to take
care of Speed and his father.
Right.
The supersonic car failed once,
and I'm going to see that
it fails completely again.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
[SPEED]
So now, I have a chance
to drive the
supersonic car again.
I'm glad to hear it, Speed.
I always knew you're
not the kind of guy
who gives up after
only one failure.
I swear, this time there
won't be any failure.
[POPS]
Ahh...
Hmm?!
[BOTH yell]
That truck almost hit us!
[POPS]
Hmm!
Get 'em, boys!
This is the perfect place
to get rid of 'em permanently!
Me and the boys
like target practicing
to see how close
we can miss you,
but now it's time to do
a little shooting for real.
Go ahead, look behind you.
[BOTH gasp]
It's all over for you, Speed.
You'll never drive
the supersonic car again.
And you'll never
build another car, Pops!
[laughs]
[SPEED]
Duck!
Pops, get down. Quick.
[yelps]
This time, I won't miss.
[THUG]
Like a sitting duck...
--[sirens]
--Huh?!
--The cops!
We'll letcha get away this time,
but not the next!
We'll finish ya.
All right, boys, c'mon.
Let's get outta here.
[engine revs]
[SPEED]
Wow, that was close!
I wonder who they are.
[NARRATOR] The second model
of the supersonic car
has been built.
And now, it stands
ready for testing.
[tires screech]
Best of luck, Speed!
[TRIXIE]
Good luck!
[POPS]
Get in the car!
[MAN chuckles]
[POPS]
Minus 15 seconds.
Nine seconds.
8... 7... 6... 5...
...4... 3... 2...
...1... Start!
[SPARKY]
Mach 0.8!
Something's wrong with the car!
What?!
Slow down, Speed!
You must stop the test!
[POPS]
Use your breaks full-force.
Stop, or the car'll break apart!
[All gasp]
[TRIXIE, SPARKY scream]
[SPEED screams]
[SPEED]
I failed again.
I've smashed
the second supersonic car.
I'm to blame for what happened.
[FERNO snickers]
[PRESIDENT] We'll conduct
an immediate investigation.
[FERNO]
Good!
I'm a qualified
engineer, gentlemen.
So I'm going to conduct the
investigation myself this time.
Pops, come over here.
Take a look in there.
Who built that part?
Tell me, I want that man's name.
Mr. Twert of the
Forthebird Motor Company.
[PRESIDENT]
Mr. Twert!
I want to ask some questions
about the part
you built for this car.
Come here.
Well? What's the
matter with you?!
Come here! Hey!
--What's the matter?!
--[POPS] Hey!
[SPEED gasps]
[PRESIDENT]
Come back here!
[SPEED]
Come back here, Twert!
Speed's gonna catch that guy.
And then once Twert starts
talking, he'll tell everything.
I've gotta stop him
from squealin'.
[SPEED grunts, TWERT groans]
You fixed it so
the car would crash.
I wanna know who's behind it.
Tell me, who put you
up to the job?
Come on, talk.
You'd better start talking
or you're gonna be sorry.
Who hired you?!
Okay, I'll talk!
[BLACKET]
Oh yeah?
--[gunshots]
--[TWERT grunts]
[SPEED gasps]
I've gotta find out who he is.
[TRIXIE]
Speed, come on, hurry!
[SPEED]
Hang on.
[SPEED] One of the other motor
companies must've hired him
to do their dirty work.
Well, if I catch him,
I'll find out.
Huh?!
This is Blacket.
Speed Racer's following me.
Intercept him, you know where.
[SPEED]
Oh, look!
[TRIXIE]
A helicopter is following us!
[SPEED]
I know!
--[SPEED gasps]
--[TRIXIE screams]
[BOTH gasp]
[SPEED]
So it's you again, huh?!
Get out of the way.
[THUG A chuckles]
We're happy to see ya again.
Remember, I promised to
finish you off the next time.
Just what company
are you working for?
Tell me!
Guess all you want
because I won't tell.
I never like to shoot a man
down when he isn't armed,
so here, take this rifle.
[SPEED]
Okay!
Now it's gonna be a fair fight.
Five of you are holding rifles,
is that a fair fight?!
[BLACKET] Sorry, you can't
have everything, Kid.
This is going to
be rough, Trixie.
You'd better get out of sight.
[TRIXIE]
Look out!
--[SPEED grunts]
--[THUGS groans]
[grunts]
[SPEED gasps]
So long, Speed.
You'll never catch me.
[SPEED]
Let's go, Trixie!
[TRIXIE]
Hurry!
[BLACKET screams]
[tires screech]
[TRIXIE gasps]
The police'll take care
of you later,
but I want to find out
who put you up to this.
Go ahead, tell me just who's
behind this whole plot, huh?
Talk, go ahead. I'll bet
it's an industrial spy
who works secretly
for another company.
If you think I'm gonna
tell you the truth,
you'd better think again, Kid.
You're just a fool
to risk your neck for
somebody else who's gonna
collect the big money
for ruining the
Vavoom Motor Company.
[SPEED]
You called for us, sir?
[PRESIDENT]
I have bad news.
All the other
employees have quit.
Now there's nobody else here.
They wouldn't follow
my orders any longer.
I understand how they feel.
After all, they worked hard
building two cars which failed,
and that I'm to blame
for that, no one else.
But sir, I'm sure
that somebody sabotaged
those supersonic
car tests both times.
And if we can get
Blacket to confess,
we'll know who's behind
the plot to ruin this company.
We've gotta find out!
Speed.
[SPEED]
Hmm?
Even if we find out
who's behind the plot,
we still may not be able to
save the Vavoom Motor Company.
We can try.
We can all try.
Let's break that speed record.
Right.
It's always been my dream
to break the speed record,
so let's try again.
If we build one more
supersonic car
and use it to break
the speed record,
we'll get so many
orders for new cars
that this company will be saved.
Come on, let's get to work.
[FERNO]
Terrible news, Mr. Tycootis.
Blacket was caught.
[TYCOOTIS]
Don't worry, Dante.
He was very well paid.
I don't think he'll talk.
Now what'll we do to ruin
the new supersonic car?
I've got a good plan
to wreck it again.
[TYCOOTIS]
Oh?
And what are you going
to do this time?
I'd rather keep it secret,
but I promise it'll be wrecked.
Sir, this will be Speed Racer's
last drive ever.
[POPS]
X minus 60 seconds...
[TYCOOTIS]
I hope everything goes well.
In other words,
that it goes badly.
[FERNO] Don't worry
about that, Mr. Tycootis.
They kept guards around
the car all the time,
but nobody was guarding
the course, get it?
That was clever thinking, Ferno.
I won't forget it.
Thanks.
Sir, here's the scheme.
It's 1:00 right now
and in 30 seconds,
the car will reach the white
line and be blown up.
[snickers]
You planted
a time bomb out there,
and in 30 seconds,
it's going to blow the car up.
Very smart.
[BOTH gasp]
[POPS]
X minus 30 seconds...
Come on, hurry!
Twenty seconds before start.
[SPRITLE]
Speed!
[SPEED]
Spritle!
Five seconds...
There's going
to be trouble, Speed.
[POPS]
...4...
[SPEED] Get outta
the car, Spritle!
[POPS]
...3... 2...
They planted a time bomb, Speed!
Start!
[SPEED] Now what were
you saying about a time bomb?!
It's set to go off
when you cross over
that white line up ahead!
[SPEED]
Oh! I see it!
But I can't stop in time!
[SPARKY]
Mach 0.5...
...0.6... 0.7... 0.8... 0.9!
Speed, you're going too fast!
You'll overheat the car!
[POPS]
He crossed the white line!
He was traveling too fast!
He was traveling at mach 1.6
when he crossed over the line!
A new record!
[ANNOUNCER]
The supersonic car
just established
a new speed record!
Congratulations, Speed.
You've saved the company
by what you've done.
[SPEED]
Thanks!
So he's established
a new speed record, eh?
And we failed;
our company's ruined.
[INSPECTOR] Mr. Tycootis of
the Forthebird Motor Company,
you're under arrest.
Come with me.
Thanks, Spritle.
Thanks for warning me
about the time bomb.
Speed, Mr. Tycootis of the
Forthebird Company was arrested
along with Mr. Ferno, and
they've confessed to everything!
[SPEED]
Hmm!
What's that?
Tycootis of the
Forthebird Company?
What could he hope to gain
by doing such terrible things?
Now he's going to spend years
in prison paying for them.
And you, Speed,
you should feel proud.
You've broken the speed record,
and you've saved our company
from going out of business now.
From now on,
with the supersonic car,
we'll break even
our own new speed record,
and our company will
be a tremendous success!
Thanks to you, Speed.
[NARRATOR] Don't miss the
next exciting episode of...
...Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪