♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR]
Speed Racer,
along with Trixie and
Sparky and the Mach 5,
are on their way to Sandoland
where Speed will compete
with the top racers
from all over the world in
the grueling Desert Race.
Where's Spritle and Chim Chim?
Staying home.
They're both pretty young
for such a long trip,
so Pops decided they'd better
not come along this time.
They sure didn't
wanna stay home.
--Speed...
--Yeah?
You know those two rascals and
how much they wanted to come.
Do you think they
might've stowed aboard?
They might be in the trunk.
I hope not.
But there's only
one way to find out.
Spritle, Chim Chim, Pops told
you you couldn't come along
so come on out of there.
[BOTH]
Oh.
[TRIXIE]
They fooled us.
I guess they stayed
home for a change.
[SPEED]
Uh-huh.
They didn't have much choice.
[SPEED]
What do you mean?
[SPARKY]
We're traveling so far.
Sparky's right.
Please be careful with the
Mach 5. It's very valuable.
We won't even give it a scratch.
Okay, let's load it on board!
[CREWMAN A]
Look out!
Hey, what's the idea?! Why don't
you look where you're going?!
He smashed it purposefully!
[chuckles]
Don't be sore about it.
I was testing the Mach 5.
Don't you mean you
were smashing it up?
[DRIVER]
Hmm...
The Mach 5's not as strong
as I thought it was.
I didn't know it could
be smashed so easily.
Listen, my name's Speed Racer.
Just who're you anyway?
[DRIVER]
Hmm.
So you're the
famous Speed Racer.
I'd been wanting to meet you
someday and race against you.
My name is Kim Jugger.
Oh! You're known as the
wildest racer in the world!
That's me all right.
And I've won every
race I've ever entered.
Look, Speed, there is
my power-packed car,
the Black Tiger.
You'll never beat it.
So don't enter the Desert Race
because you don't have a chance.
Thanks for your advice,
but I'm entering the race and
I'll beat you with the Mach 5.
That's what you think.
I'm going to make you
eat those words, Speed.
--[SPEED] Oh, yeah?
--Don't!
You'd better hold
him back, young lady,
otherwise I'll beat the
daylights out of him.
We're all ready
to load the Mach 5.
Hold it! Load my car, the Black
Tiger on board the ship first.
[BOTH]
But...
Go ahead. And if you
put one scratch on her,
I'll make sure you're
fired from your job.
[BOTH]
Yes, sir.
We were here first!
[SPARKY growls]
[CREWMAN A]
Okay!
[ANNOUNCER] Flight number
326 for Arabia and Sandoland
leaving shortly.
Passengers for Arabia and
Sandoland may now go on board
through gate number five.
Flight number 326 for Arabia
and Sandoland leaving shortly.
Passengers for Arabia and
Sandoland may now go on board
through gate number five.
Hiya, Stewardess. Heh, oh...
You know how jealous
some girls are.
[STEWARDESS]
I certainly do.
Six, Seven, Eight, I lost count.
Hmm...
[STEWARDESS]
Would you like some candy?
[TRIXIE]
Oh, thank you.
Wow! Thanks, Stewardess!
[STEWARDESS]
Candy?
[KIDS shouting]
[CHIM CHIM bellows]
[shrieks]
[SPRITLE]
Run, Chim Chim!
Hide!
Ah!
[gasps]
[SPRITLE]
Look!
[gibbering]
[SPRITLE]
This car's the Black Tiger.
I hear something.
[SPRITLE]
Hmm?
[ticking]
[SPRITLE]
Shh...
What's he doing?
[SPRITLE]
Duck!
[SPRITLE screams]
[growling]
[MAN]
Come out of there!
[screams]
[laughing]
[SPRITLE]
C'mon, Chim Chim!
[bell rings]
[STEWARDESS] We are now
landing in Sandoland.
Fasten your seatbelts, please.
[STEWARDESS]
Watch your step, please.
[MOTHER]
Stay together, children,
so no one gets lost
in this strange land.
[MOTHER]
Keep close to mama.
Terribly sorry!
[crying]
Oh, the poor,
precious little baby.
--You know it was an accident.
--Give him some milk.
Then have some milk,
you precious, little thing.
[CHIM CHIM growls]
[screams]
[SPEED]
Huh?
It's Spritle!
And Chim Chim!
[SPRITLE]
Run!
[SPEED]
Spritle, wait! Stop!
[SPRITLE]
I can't!
Look out, Speed!
[thud]
[SPRITLE whines]
Naughty boy.
[ticking]
[CREWMEN scream]
[KIM]
Huh?!
[SPEED, TRIXIE gasp]
My Black Tiger!
It blew up!
[TRIXIE]
Who could have done it?!
[KIM]
Could they have left this? Huh?
That's mine! Oh,
please, give it back!
I dropped it when I was hiding.
Not so fast, kid.
This is evidence and I'm
going to hang on to it.
It proves that you
were inside my car
and you could've
planted a time bomb.
That's nothing but a lie!
Spritle wouldn't do
a thing like that!
Take it back!
[KIM]
That bomb I think he planted
smashed my special brake system!
You put your brother
up to the job, Speed,
because I smashed
into the Mach 5!
That's a stupid idea!
Listen! Why don't you admit
that you're the one who
planted the bomb, right?!
[SPRITLE]
No, not right! I didn't do it!
Leave my brother alone, Kim!
I want him to tell
me the truth! Huh?!
[growling]
[yells]
Hey!
You want to fight?!
[SPEED] Well, it might do
you some good. Come on!
Easy, Speed! Don't fight him!
I've got to. He's been
asking for it all along.
[TRIXIE]
Speed, be careful. Be careful!
[yells]
C'mon, Speed! Give it
to him! A left and a right!
Do you give up?
[groans]
[KIM]
You haven't seen anything yet.
[grumbling]
[SPEED]
Huh? Oh!
Oh... Oh...
[KIM] Our fight isn't over.
But here, Kid, keep it.
[SPRITLE]
Oh!
[SPEED]
Kim, who are these men?
What are they doing here?
They came here to
see me, that's all.
[SPEED]
You?
[KIM] That's all I can
tell you right now.
And as for damaging my car,
I still think you did it.
And one way or another, I'm
going to make you pay for it.
[SPEED]
We had nothing to do with it
and you're a liar to say we did!
[KIM]
You're the liar!
No, Speed! Let him go!
Take it easy!
When I see you again, I'll
beat you in the race, Speed.
[SPEED]
Before the race,
I've got to prove to him that
we didn't sabotage his car.
I've got to...
[NARRATOR] This is Puba, the
fabulous capital of Sandoland.
The Imperial Hotel, where
the Mach 5 Go Team is staying.
[SPEED] Why didn't you tell
me this whole story before,
Spritle?
I'm sorry. I forgot
about it, Speed.
Oh, you just forgot.
So when you were in the freight
compartment of the plane,
you saw a mysterious
one-eyed man come in
and put something into Kim's
racing car the Black Tiger.
[SPRITLE]
Mm-hmm!
[SPEED]
That's all I have to know.
[TRIXIE]
Where're you going?
To see Kim.
He should be somewhere in this
mysterious, fabulous city,
and I've got to find him.
I've gotta tell him
what Spritle told us.
It proves that I'm innocent.
I'll see you all later.
[SPEED] I'm sorry. I was in
a hurry and I didn't see you!
I didn't see you either.
[SPEED] I'm looking for
a racer named Kim.
Is he staying at this hotel?
The one that owns
the Black Tiger car?
[SPEED]
Yes.
[BELLHOP]
Yes, I know him very well.
He's a fast and clever racer.
But he's gone to his homeland,
the Flathill Country.
I am most sorry,
but now you will not find
him anywhere in Sandoland.
He left quickly.
--[BELLHOP] I know.
--[SPEED] Why?
Well, the way I heard it,
somebody blew his car up
and there's no way to
get it repaired in time
for the big Desert Race.
I wish there was some way
to find out who did it.
[SPEED] So do I. Thanks
for the information.
[BELLHOP]
Hmm... Hmm?
[TRIXIE]
Cheer up, Speed.
I can't, Trixie.
We know you're innocent.
The only way to prove that
is to find the man who did it.
[SPEED]
I'll prove it.
I don't have to do things
like that to win races.
I can win them fair and square.
I've gotta convince Kim
I didn't blow up his car.
[TRIXIE]
Good evening!
[gasps]
I'm going with you.
Hop in, Speed.
You're going to Flathill
Country to see Kim.
I can read your mind.
So can we, can't we, Chim Chim?
[TRIXIE]
Oh!
[SPEED] I can hardly see
in this sandstorm.
Speed, I think this
storm's getting worse.
[SPEED]
Mm-hm.
[SPEED] We'll wait
here till it blows over.
It's over. I was afraid we'd
be buried under the sand.
Whee! It's the biggest
sand pile I've ever seen!
Oh, look over there!
What?
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[SPRITLE screams]
[RIDER A]
Charge!
[gasps]
Those camels are the fastest
I've ever seen anywhere!
[TRIXIE]
Oh...
Here comes some more!
Wow! A whole army of them!
My sand pile was
never like this!
[TRIXIE]
Oh!
[growls]
Stop that car!
Okay, it's time we
counterattack, Chim Chim.
Pass the ammo to me!
[RIDERS yelp]
We've got help of some kind,
and it's coming from our trunk.
Okay, I need more ammunition.
Aw, you mean we're
out of it, Chim Chim?
But I know we've got
a couple of things left,
so we may as well use 'em.
[growls]
Ah! Delicious!
[BOTH gasp]
[RIDER A laughing]
[RIDER A]
We've got them now!
[gasps]
[RIDER A] Tell me...
Where are you going? Well?
To Flathill Country to
visit a racer named Kim.
Kim.
[RIDER B, RIDER C]
Kim?
We have to talk to him.
Do you know him?
We are members of the
Army of Flathill Country,
and, if you permit us, we
will take you to visit him.
Oh, why didn't you say so?
We didn't know you were
Flathill Army Soldiers.
If you had told us
that in the first place,
I wouldn't have been scared.
All right, follow us.
Wait! We were told that Flathill
Country is to the south,
that it's that way.
We know very well
where Flathill Country is.
Just be quiet and follow us.
I've got to see Kim, I must.
And who says you're
really from Flathill, huh?
[RIDER A] We're not from
Flathill Country now,
but we used to be.
If you want to know the
real truth, I will tell you.
Right now, my men
and I, and others,
are fighting against
Flathill Country.
--[SPEED] Huh?
--Well...
...that means that you're
nothing but a bunch of rebels.
[RIDER A] Flathill Country was
being ruined by those in power.
Only a revolution can change
things for the better,
and so we hope to save
our beloved country.
Now don't ask any more
questions and follow me.
You are suspected
of being spies,
so I must take you to
our fortress. Come.
[SPEED] Spies?
What're you talking about?
We just wanna see Kim.
You can make up your alibi
when we get to the fortress.
Let's go.
--[TRIXIE] Oh!
--Kim!
[KIM]
Hello, Speed.
We meet again as
I said we would.
Why do you belong to
the rebel army, Kim?
My father commands
all of the rebel soldiers.
It's good of you to
travel all this way,
though I still think you're
a coward for what you did.
I swear, Kim, I had nothing to
do with your car being blown up.
And what's more,
he didn't even order somebody
else to do the job for him.
[KIM] That's not true! You
ordered that kid to do it.
I found the evidence, remember?
I know that you, Speed, are
guilty of trying to bomb my car!
Men, put Speed Racer into jail!
[SPEED]
No!
Wait!
I can point out the person
who blew up your car!
He's the man standing
right behind you, Kim!
[MAN growls]
My brother Spritle
was hiding on the plane
and saw him plant the time bomb!
And I can prove you're the one!
Chim Chim scratched your face!
Don't you remember that?!
[MAN]
Huh?!
What are you waiting for?!
You heard Kim's orders!
Throw them in jail! All of them!
[GO TEAM gasping]
Burn the Mach 5! Burn the car!
[TRIXIE]
Oh... Oh...
Kim, listen! You've got to
believe me, I'm not lying!
Kim, please! Trust me, Kim!
[NARRATOR]
Prisoners... Can they escape?
And what of Ali Ben Schemer?
[BEN SCHEMER chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
Is this the end of the road
for Speed Racer and his friends?
Is there any way
out of this trap?
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪