♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR]
The city of Dominico,
where the South American
Grand Prix is being held.
[MAN pants]
[engines revving]
[yells]
[ANNOUNCER]
Señors and señoritras,
the cars are now in the last lap
of the South American
Grand Prix.
They are coming toward
the finish line.
And Speed Racer in the
supercharged Formula 1
is leading by one car length!
[TRIXIE, SPARKY, SPRITLE]
Go, Speed! Go! Go!
[ANNOUNCER]
Señor Speed Racer
in the supercharged
Formula 1 wins!
[CROWD cheers]
[SPARKY chuckling]
[TRIXIE growls]
Don't think I'm jealous
because she kissed him!
[gasps]
I wish I could win a race
so some beautiful señorita
would dance for me like that.
[SPEED chuckles]
Olé!
[WOMAN shrieks]
--[SPEED gasps]
--[gasps]
[PEOPLE murmuring]
Help me, please!
[groans]
[DANCER]
José!
José, what happened?
[JOSÉ groans]
[DANCER]
José!
Oh, José!
[JOSÉ groaning]
Here, Marie, this serum...
Be careful with it.
[JOSÉ groans]
[MARIE gasps]
[wails, sobs]
[engine sputtering]
[SPEED gasps]
[MARIE groaning]
[MARIE gasps]
[gasps]
[SPEED grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[gasps]
[grunting continues]
[yelps]
[SPEED gasps]
[SPEED]
Come on! Run!
[gasps]
[screams]
Speed! Hop in, hurry!
[SPEED]
Hang on!
Ah.
[THUG A] The bull has given up.
They were too fast for him.
Si, let's go.
[SPRITLE]
Speed! Speed!
[SPARKY]
Hi, Trixie.
That was quick driving, Speed.
You're as nimble
as a bull fighter.
[SPEED laughs]
Olé!
I watched those
two men run away.
They just gave up.
Thank you, Speed.
You don't realize
what you've done.
[SPEED]
Hmm?
[SPARKY]
Huh?
Those men tried to get
their hands on this serum.
Serum?
[MARIE]
Why, yes.
My brother Juan was
bitten by a poison snake
and he must be given this serum.
[SPEED]
Oh, I see.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, in the
distant village of Tonado...
If he can only hold out
a little longer,
maybe the serum will arrive
and he will be saved.
Juan, you mustn't
kick the goatskin.
You're head of our village
and we wouldn't know
what to do without you!
[JUAN groans]
In only three more hours,
it will be too late.
I wonder what's
taking José so long.
He should have arrived here
with the serum.
[FRANSCO] I think I'll
go outside and watch for him.
[THUG B]
Hey, Fransco.
[FRANSCO]
Huh?
[THUG B]
Fransco, over here.
Bad news, Señor.
[FRANSCO]
What do you mean?
Our men failed.
You mean they weren't
able to get rid of José?!
[THUG B]
No, Señor...
They got him,
but they were unable
to get their hands on the serum.
[FRANSCO]
Huh?!
Why not? I gave them
explicit orders.
But Marie got the serum.
[FRANSCO] Huh?!
Those bumbling stone heads.
What are they trying to do,
help me or make sure
my plans fail?!
What's the matter with them?!
I'll make up for them.
I'll have the poisonous snake
bite Juan again.
And maybe he'll
kick the goatskin
before his sister arrives
with the serum.
You can't use the same
method on him again!
I will just have to stop
his sister Marie Posa
from getting here in time.
[THUG B]
Hmm... You're right.
[FRANSCO]
Uh-huh.
If Marie fails to arrive
within the next three hours
with the serum,
Juan will kick the goatskin
and I will take his place
as mayor of this village.
And the treasure
hidden here will be mine!
[laughs]
[SPARKY] Okay, the car's
all tuned and all set to go.
Good luck!
Speed, won't you take me
along with you, please?
I'm sorry, Trixie, but you know
there's room for
only two in the Mach 5.
And Marie's gotta go so that
she can help her brother!
Oh! Yes, you're right.
[SPEED]
Now, Trixie, listen.
Stay here in the city
and wait for me.
[SPRITLE snickers]
[SPRITLE] At least there's
room for us, Chim Chim.
[TRIXIE]
So long! Good luck!
Sparky, where's
Spritle and Chim Chim?
I don't see them.
They were here
a minute ago; I saw them!
Uh-oh, they're gone all right!
I'll bet I know where they went.
They're in the truck of the car.
[giggles]
Well, I can't blame 'em.
I think they're smart.
[SPARKY]
Huh?!
I wonder why they tried
to stop that man
from bringing serum
to your brother, Marie.
So do I.
Someone doesn't
want him to recover.
Can you remember
if he has any enemies?
I can't think of any.
In fact, everyone in the village
likes my brother very much.
Then why did they try
to get rid of him
by attempting to see that the
serum didn't reach him in time?
I don't know. I have no idea.
There's something very strange
about this whole thing.
[MARIE] This bridge
doesn't look very strong.
Do you think we can make it?
This is the only bridge across
this river for a hundred miles;
we've gotta try.
Here goes.
[MARIE, SPEED gasp]
[SPEED]
Hang on!
[BOTH gasp]
--[SPEED gasps]
--[MARIE screams]
[gasps]
There's something
funny out there.
I wonder where
Speed's driving us.
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[SPRITLE]
Water!
What's happened? Did the
Mach 5 turn into a submarine?
Hmm?
I wonder if Speed knows.
Hey, Speed!
[MARIE]
Speed! Speed, wake up!
We're caught in the river!
[SPEED groans]
[MARIE]
Speed, do something.
[SPEED]
Wha--?
Look out the window.
Look what's happening to us.
[SPEED gasps]
[creaking]
Wow.
Now I've got to figure out
a way for us to reach
that bank over there.
And we've gotta work fast
or we'll never get to your
brother in time with the serum!
Maybe I can do something
with that tree.
[FRANSCO] He has only
an hour and half left.
[snickers]
I figured something out, but I'm
not sure it's going to work.
Marie, there's a letter marked
"G" on the steering column.
Push the button.
All right.
Bullseye! But this rope
may not be strong enough.
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
--[SPEED] Huh?
--[MARIE gasps]
Chim Chim! I didn't know
you were in the car.
And I'll bet Spritle's
in the trunk.
How'd you guess?
Listen, Speed. You gotta
do something and fast.
I'm going to, Spritle.
I'm glad you're here.
I need your help!
[splash]
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[SPEED]
Okay, Chim Chim! Go!
[SPRITLE]
Keep going, Chim Chim! Go on!
Good work, Chim Chim!
Hang on!
[engine revs]
You've done it, Chim Chim!
Just one more hour
and they'll be too late.
[THUG B] Señor Fransco,
we weren't able to stop her.
Huh... You mean
you failed again?
Yes, Marie's on
her way here with
someone in a very fast,
specially built racing car.
[BOTH gasp]
--[MARIE gasps]
--[SPEED grunts]
[SPEED gasps]
They almost got us;
that was much too close!
We're stuck though, Marie.
We've gotta move those rocks
out of the way there.
Okay.
[SPEED gasps]
They've got us in a trap!
What'll we do?
Those men are from my village.
They don't want us
to reach your brother in time.
But we've got to.
He needs that serum.
[SPEED]
Marie.
Yes?
Half an hour left.
Speed, I didn't
come along for nothing.
Now it's my turn to help.
I'll carry the serum.
[yelps]
[chuckles]
[JUAN groans]
[VIEJO] Hang on, Juan.
The serum will be here soon.
Let's distract them
so Spritle can get away.
[THUG C]
Get them!
--[gunshots]
--After them!
[SPRITLE]
Get ready to run.
Stop them!
Don't let them get away!
[MARIE, SPEED gasp]
[SPEED] We'll never be
able to climb up there!
[BOTH gasp]
[THUGS snickering]
[THUG D] Now you will not
deliver the serum in time.
Get out of the way.
We've got to reach my brother!
We have orders to see
that you don't reach him.
You'll never see him again.
Who gave you
the order to stop us?
Soon, all the treasure in
the village will belong to us.
But to get it, we don't want
your brother to live.
So he mustn't get the serum.
Give it to me.
We haven't got the serum.
Liar!
[SPEED groans]
I want you to
give me that serum!
--Hand it over!
--It's in my car.
I'll have to go and get it.
Okay, go ahead.
But you better hurry.
Come on, hurry up!
[THUGS grunting]
[SPEED yells]
[THUGS groaning]
Nice shooting!
Come on, Juan.
You must try to hold
out a little longer.
We need you here in the village!
Why hasn't your sister
brought the serum?
What's keeping her?
[FRANSCO] You might as
well give up, Viejo.
The serum will never get here
in time to save him.
Don't even say that, Fransco.
Juan is a great man
and he will hold out
until his sister brings
the snake bite serum.
[FRANSCO chuckles]
I don't think his sister
is even trying
to bring the serum
here to save him.
[VIEJO]
I can't believe that.
[FRANSCO] Would I lie to you?
Me, honest Francisco Fransco?
The serum will never get here.
Never.
See you at the funeral.
Why is Fransco so happy when
Juan is in such bad shape?
I don't get it.
[gasps]
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
Everything's gonna
be okay now.
Chim Chim and I
brought the serum!
Oh, wonderful news!
Now that Juan is gone, I'll be
the mayor of this village.
Yes, from now on, I'll be
the man in charge here.
I will run the village in a way
that'll make you happy, I think.
[SPRITLE]
Don't let him be mayor!
[FRANSCO]
Huh?!
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
You! Boy! What do you want?!
[SPRITLE]
Listen, everybody!
Juan was not bitten
accidentally by the snake!
It was part of a plot so he
could take over the village!
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
Shut up! You have no evidence!
You can't prove that, Kid!
No, but your plot failed!
[FRANSCO]
Huh?!
--[VILLAGER A] The Mayor!
--[VILLAGER B] It's Juan!
[VILLAGER C]
He's alive!
[FRANSCO]
Huh?!
Thanks to that serum,
he's all right.
And he'll continue
to be our mayor.
Fransco, all you want is to rob
this village of its treasures,
but you can't get away with it!
Punish the renegade!
Yeah, send him away!
Get out of here!
Wait. You can't get rid
of me so easily.
I'm too powerful for that, Juan.
My men have gotten rid
of your sister, Marie!
Huh? Marie!
[FRANSCO cackles]
[FRANSCO gasps]
[MARIE]
Juan!
Juan, my brother!
--Marie!
--You're safe!
[MARIE sobs]
Spritle, you sure did
a great job.
Well, it wasn't so tough,
was it, Chim Chim?
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
You haven't heard
the last of me.
Since you won't let me
be mayor of the village,
there won't be any village.
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
[SPEED gasps]
[VILLAGER D] Fire!
They're burning the village!
[bull bellows]
[screams]
Fransco has stampeded the bulls!
[SPRITLE growls]
[FRANSCO cackles]
Now let the village
burn to the ground
and be crushed
beneath the bulls.
It doesn't matter to me.
[VILLAGERS scream]
[FRANSCO cackles]
[VIEJO] Fransco's
getting away; after him!
[horse neighs]
[FRANSCO] You shouldn't have
followed me here, Kid.
--[yells]
--[SPEED gasps]
[FRANSCO grunting]
[SPEED gasps]
[FRANSCO chuckles]
[horse neighs]
[FRANSCO gasps]
[screams]
Listen to me!
Tomorrow, we will begin
rebuilding the village,
and it will be
even better than before.
[ALL]
Olé!
And if you think of
anything we can do,
we'll be glad to help!
Thank you, Speed.
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[thud]
[ALL laugh]
[NARRATOR] See the next exciting
episode of... Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪