♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR] Somewhere deep in the
hills of old bonnie Scotland...
[flute plays]
[flute playing continues]
Huh?! Ah-hah...
Ah, beloved monster, the time
has come for you to wake up.
[MAN]
The storm has grown stronger;
it's directly overhead.
And I've been waiting
impatiently 22 years
for this very moment!
Now, now you shall be awakened
and the world will see
you for the first time!
[MAN cackles]
One more lightning bolt
and you will come to life!
[MAN]
Ah...
At last, the Monster Car
has come to life!
[MAN laughs]
To county Burrup!
Ruin the countryside;
do all the damage you can!
[laughing]
Lightning, keep giving
power to my car!
[MAN laughs]
A Monster Car!
[POLICEMAN A]
Hmm...
There's somethin' up ahead!
It's too big to be a truck!
It's goin' a hundred and forty!
That's much too fast in
this weather. Let's stop him.
We're about to crash!
[POLICEMAN B] A dangerous
driver! You all right?!
[POLICEMAN A]
Aye... I was lucky.
[POLICEMAN B]
Me, too.
I've never seen a vehicle
like that before.
And I hope I've seen it
for the last time.
[POLICMEAN B]
Mm-hmm.
It looked as if it was headin'
for the racing circuit.
[SPRITLE gasps]
[SPRITLE]
Ah!
Look, Chim Chim!
It must be an earthquake!
Turn on the light, Spritle!
[SPEED]
What is it?! What's going on?!
[BOTH gasp]
[SPRITLE gasps]
[SPARKY whimpers]
Oh! The whole place
is coming down!
Let's see what's
happening outside!
[PEOPLE yelling]
A monster!
A car of some kind!
We're bein' attacked by
some kind of monster tank!
[SPARKY] Wow!
There it is, whatever it is!
[SPEED] That's what's
causing the earthquake!
Maybe we've been caught
in the middle of a war!
[TRIXIE]
I hope not!
It looks pretty bad to me. We'd
better get out of the hotel.
I'd better go get
the Mach 5, Pops,
before something happens to it!
[POPS] No, Speed! There isn't
time! You're liable to get hurt!
Speed, come back! Ah!
Come on! Let's get out of here!
[SPARKY]
Run!
[gasps]
Huh?!
[engine revving]
Maybe I can find out what
that thing is. I'll follow it.
[SPEED]
It's got tremendous power.
I wonder who's
operating it and why.
[screams]
Stop! Don't come any
closer or we'll open fire
and you'll be destroyed!
Stop! This is your last chance!
Stop right there!
Get ready, men! Fire!
Ah!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[REPORTER] It has been
learned that the Monster Car
came from the ruins of a castle
in the old bonnie hills
of county McMac.
When police checked
the ruined castle,
they found a retired
scientist, Dr. McFife,
and took him to the local
constabulary for questioning.
The army has been called in
to try to stop the Monster Car,
but so far, they have
failed miserably.
Now for the exciting
world of sports!
The great Tweed and
Tartan Grand Prix
for which Speed Racer and
other well-known drivers
have come to our bonnie
country has been cancelled
since the Monster Car wrecked
the bonnie racing course!
I'll bet Speed's following
the Monster Car
to find out more about it.
Boy, I hope he's not,
because it's too dangerous!
The army failed miserably,
so who knows what
it might do to him?!
--[SPRITLE gasps]
--[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
Ah! The Mach 5!
[TRIXIE]
Oh no!
[POPS]
Speed! What happened?!
--[TRIXIE] Speed!
--[SPARKY] He looks hurt!
Are you all right?!
Come on, Son! Wake up!
[TRIXIE gasps]
[SPEED groans]
Speed's coming out of it.
He'll be all right.
[SPRITLE]
Hiya, Speedy!
We're glad you
weren't hurt, Speed!
[SPEED] That Monster Car's
the most amazing vehicle
I've ever seen!
Didn't I warn you that
you'd get into trouble
if you went near it?!
[SPARKY] Now we're gonna
have to put the Mach 5
back on its four wheels again.
I wonder who could've
built such a monster car!
[SPARKY]
And I wonder who could drive it!
[SPARKY grunting]
By the way, Speed,
the racing circuit was
destroyed by the Monster Car
and the Grand Prix's
been called off!
Well, that's too bad.
I was sure I was going to win.
It's just an unlucky break.
I hope they rebuild the track.
Who's that?
[tires squeal]
Excuse me, sir, I'm looking
for Mr. Pops Racer.
[POPS]
Well, that's me.
I must ask you to come to
police headquarters, Mr. Racer.
Huh...?
[ALL gasp]
[SPRITLE]
Gee, Pops, are you under arrest?
What did you do wrong now?
--Quiet!
--Ah!
[POLICEMAN C]
Hmm?
[laughs]
I'm sorry, I didn't
mean to frighten ya!
We just need you
down at headquarters
so that you can tell us how
that Monster Car might work.
After all,
you're supposed to be the most
expert car expert in the world!
[POPS] As a matter
of fact, that's right!
How smart you are to realize it!
[laughs]
[CHIM CHIM gibbering]
Sorry, Chim Chim, but they
told us we'd have to stay out.
[laughs]
You're wrong, gentlemen, there's
no one driving the Monster Car.
And there's no one
who can stop it, either!
And soon, it will destroy all!
All of county Burrup!
[laughing]
Dr. McFife was a
brilliant scientist,
and I believe he built and
activated that Monster Car
just before he went
completely whacky.
[POPS]
Judging by what Dr. McFife said
about no one being in the car,
I figure that the
car's being operated
by its own built-in
electronic brain.
Electronic brain?
That would explain
why the doctor said
that no one will be
able to stop the car!
[CHIEF]
It makes sense!
[POPS] Hmm, and that electronic
brain has been programmed
to keep the car attacking and
destroying everything in sight!
It'll be impossible to stop!
[CHIEF] Let me show ya
something on this map.
The reports coming in here
to police headquarters
indicate that the Monster Car
is following this path
across both land and water.
What? The Monster Car's
able to cross water?
Yes, it obviously can.
It must cross Crooked Straits
to follow the course on the map.
Poor Mr. McFife must've had some
grudge against Burrup County
to build a monster car
and program it
to create mayhem
throughout Burrup.
[POPS]
Hmm...
Part of the trouble is
that the electronic brain
probably has been
programmed to attack anybody
who tries to attack
the Monster Car.
Western Burrup County
is making elaborate plans
to fight the Monster Car if and
when it crosses Crooked Straits
and resumes
its terrible attacks.
Pops, that might be the best
time to try to attack the car.
While it's submerged
in the water,
it will be weaker and slower
and more vulnerable, I hope.
[POPS]
You're right, Speed!
That may be the only chance
to successfully attack it.
[TRIXIE]
But won't it be too dangerous?
[POPS]
Possibly.
I will send our Navy after it.
We'll attack it with submarines.
[SPEED]
Oh...
[POPS] Speed, before
the car enters the water,
let's see if we can
spot its weakest point.
--[SPEED] That's a good idea...!
--Come on!
[SPEED]
Right.
[TRIXIE]
Be careful!
They're not taking us with 'em.
Come on, Spritle,
we'll cross Crooked
Straits in my helicopter!
Oh boy! Let's go!
You know, Pops, I found
out that the Monster Car
has rocket engines.
Then it's fueled by
metal alcohol, I bet.
[SPEED] And that stuff
burns pretty fast,
so its fuel supply
can't last long.
It'll run out of gas before it
can get across Crooked Straits.
You may be right, Speed.
I sure hope you are.
It won't be long
before we find out.
Here comes the Monster Car now!
It's going to try to
cross the straits! Huh?!
[gasps]
[POPS]
They're going to bomb the car!
The car's equipped
with a deflector ray!
Ah! Duck, Speed! Get down!
[BOTH gasp]
It's headed for the lighthouse,
and that's needed to guide
the ships through the straits
so they won't crash
on the rocks!
Pops, what's the car
doing with that pipe?
I dunno!
It started up again!
[POPS]
Hmm...
[SPEED]
Let's go!
[POPS]
Hmm...
Now I remember.
Speed, this used to be a fueling
station for passing freighters.
Years ago, they'd
anchor offshore
and the oil would be
pumped out of them.
The only way we can
stop that car now
is sneak on and put it
out of commission.
Okay, then.
Speed, where're you going?!
I'm gonna try to sneak
on board the Monster Car!
Wait, Speed! Stop!
Speed!
[whirring]
Speed just drove the
Mach 5 into the water!
[SPEED]
Oh...
We've spotted the Monster Car!
Fire torpedoes!
Idiot! We must destroy that car!
How I'm gonna get in it?
So that's it!
There's a door on the bottom!
[COMMANDER B]
Uh-oh!
Get ready, take aim!
[COMMANDER B]
Fire!
He'll never be able to
get across those straits
in the Mach 5.
He shouldn't have tried to.
I'm worried.
Look! What's that down there?
It's our car.
[ALL gasp]
[TRIXIE] Oh, Speed, we're
so glad you're all right!
[POPS]
Learn anything?
Yes, Pops, I sure did.
I found out how we
can get on board
the Monster Car to stop it.
There's a door that opens
in the bottom of it.
Then come on, let's report
what you've found out
to the Defense Office
before it's too late.
--[PEOPLE screaming]
--Mama, Mama!
Mama! I want my Mama!
[GIRL sobs]
Where is she, where's my Mama?!
Quick, help her!
That's my little girl out there!
That's my daughter! Save her!
[GIRL screams]
They're taking her away!
Come back, Monster!
[BOARD LEADER] This is an
Electronic Brain Rattler.
It will scramble the thoughts
of an electronic brain
for a few minutes.
It might scramble the electronic
brain of the Monster Car,
at least for a short time.
Let's hope so.
We'd better try it right now.
But how will we make it work?
[BOARD LEADER] Someone must get
very close to the Monster Car.
The closer, the better.
Then they must try
to work this rattler.
Of course, it will be a very
dangerous mission,
but it's our only chance!
Sir, I have
important information
about the Monster Car!
Dr. McFife has just revealed
that when the car
reaches the center
of our military fortifications,
it will blow itself up!
The explosives inside
the car are so powerful,
that if they go off,
they'll destroy almost all
of what's left of county Burrup!
That car is a very powerful
rolling bomb! That is all, sir.
[BOARD LEADER]
That is more than enough!
There's no time to lose!
We must act immediately!
We must use this brain rattler!
[CHAIRMAN D] But who's going
to take it close enough
to the Monster Car so that it'll
work? Who's brave enough?
[BOARD LEADER]
Hmm...
Sir, a young girl was just
taken aboard the car!
Gentlemen, you've just
heard the latest report!
We've gotta do
something right away!
[SPEED]
Sir?
[BOARD LEADER]
Yes, Speed?
I wanna go on the mission!
[CHAIRMEN gasping]
That little girl's
gotta be rescued, Pops,
and maybe I can do
it with my Mach 5!
It's dangerous!
Danger is one thing
Speed's not scared of!
[TRIXIE]
Be careful, Speed!
[SPRITLE]
Hey!
I've gotta hurry!
--[TRIXIE gasps]
--Good luck!
There's the
Monster Car up ahead!
Don't be scared,
you're all right.
And I'll have you
out in no time.
I'll use the rattler.
[SPEED]
Ah...
[SPEED] The rattler is
scrambling the electronic brain,
but how do I make the car stop?
Oh, there's Speed! Hey, Speed,
come on, wake up! Come on!
[CHIM CHIM gibbering]
Wake up, Speed! Hurry, wake up
before the Monster Car explodes!
Wake up!
What're you doing here?
I just wanted to help!
You can't leave Chim Chim and me
behind when you're in danger!
Listen, Spritle!
We've gotta act fast!
Everybody, get into
the Mach 5! Hurry up!
What's the matter, Speed?!
I can't get the Monster Car's
bottom door to open!
Hang on, the bottom door's
finally beginning to open!
[ALL scream]
[gasps]
It's completely destroyed!
[ALL gasp]
[SPEED]
Huh?
Ah! There's Pops
and Trixie and Sparky!
[GIRL]
Oh!
And there's Mama!
Mama!
[MOTHER]
You're all right!
Speed, you've made me so proud!
And I'm proud of Spritle and
Chim Chim who helped me out.
[SPRITLE]
Thanks, Speedy!
You two might've been hurt! That
was no mission for children!
We won't do it again...
[POPS, SPARKY laughing]
Thank you, Speed!
Thank you for all you've done
to save county Burrup.
If it hadn't been for
your great bravery,
we would've been
totally destroyed.
Everyone here is
grateful to you.
[NARRATOR]
Be sure to see the next
thrilling episode
of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪