♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR]
High in the alpine mountains.
[TRIXIE]
Quick turn to the right.
Another.
Careful of the tree up ahead.
In exactly 200 yards, you've
gotta make a turn to the left.
[SPEED]
Trixie and I are competing in
the Monte Carlo Rally.
Snow has brought visibility
down almost to zero.
The only thing I can depend on
are Trixie's instructions.
We have 300 miles to go
before we reach Monte Carlo.
If we get there safely and
without being disqualified,
we'll be allowed to
compete in the Grand Prix
the day after tomorrow.
[screams]
[TRIXIE] That sign should say
a sharp turn to the right.
Get ready.
[SPEED grunts]
He's not taking part
in the Alpine Rally.
[gasps]
[BOTH scream]
[BOTH grunt]
[TRIXIE gasping]
[NARRATOR]
In Monaco, the rally has ended,
and the cars inspected
to see if they qualify
to enter the Grand Prix.
The headlamp is smashed.
This car is disqualified.
[ENGINEER A]
Mm-hmm.
[ENGINEER B] The engine
is not perfectly sealed,
deduct 300 points.
The car is disqualified.
All lights are okay;
mirror okay.
[ENGINEER C]
Mm-hmm.
[ENGINEER D]
Hey, what's this?
Hmm.
[NARRATOR]
At police headquarters,
Speed and Trixie try to identify
the man who attacked them.
[SPEED]
No, not this one either.
Or this.
[TRIXIE]
None of them look like the man.
Not this man either.
[TRIXIE] I had no idea there
were so many criminals
wanted by the police!
[SPEED] I don't see
his picture, Inspector.
[TRIXIE]
I guess we're out of luck.
You said that the man
pulled a gun on you
and then forced you to
drive him to Monte Carlo, eh?
Interesting.
He could be a bank robber.
Hmm...
[TRIXIE gasps]
There's the man!
[SPEED]
What?! Let me see.
[DUBIOUS gasps]
[SPEED]
That's him all right.
It says, "Mr. Fastbucks
staying in Monte Carlo
has been a heavy winner
at roulette."
[PEOPLE chattering]
[DEALER]
And there...
Thirteen, red!
[ALL]
Oh no! Not number 13 again!
[PEOPLE groaning]
[DEALER] Place your bets,
ladies and gentlemen.
Place your bets.
And to the lucky gentleman
who again is the winner,
here you are, monsieur.
Place your bets,
ladies and gentlemen!
Let us continue,
ladies and gentlemen.
Place your bets again.
You can put all
my chips on number 13.
--[PEOPLE gasp]
--[WOMAN A] Again?!
That's all the bets this time.
[DEALER]
Number 13, red, wins again!
[ALL gasp, chatter]
[FASTBUCKS chuckles]
[cackles]
[DUBIOUS]
Mr. Fastbucks!
[FASTBUCKS]
Huh?!
Mr. Fastbucks, I'm police
inspector Anton Dubious.
Well, I'm pleased to meet you,
Inspector Dubious.
However, why are you
interrupting my roulette?
Do I look familiar to you?
Didn't we meet
during that rally?
Sorry, young man,
but I never saw you before.
[laughs]
This young man
is making a mistake.
Obviously, I couldn't have
met him during the car rally
because I've been playing
roulette with all of you
the past two nights.
And during the day,
I've been sleeping
and dreaming of money.
[ALL laugh]
This young man looked at every
picture on our wanted list,
and then identified you from
a photograph in the newspaper.
He says you're the man.
The next time you come here
and interrupt my game,
Inspector, you'd better
have more evidence
than the word of a young man
who's obviously a liar.
[TRIXIE gasps]
Well, I can identify you, too!
You have evidence, I trust.
Well, let's hear
about it, Miss Smarty.
[TRIXIE gasps]
[SPEED]
Careful! I'm warning you!
[FASTBUCKS laughs]
The right arm of the man
I saw was wounded.
That's true.
Come on, let's see how well
you work your right arm.
[FASTBUCKS]
Gladly.
See? It's perfect.
[chuckles]
Now, if you're through
with me, get out of here.
Let me warn you, young man,
to be careful in
that race tomorrow.
You never know,
it'll be very dangerous,
so look out.
All right, let's get on
with the game.
As you can see,
that young man didn't know
what he was talking about.
[BELLBOY]
Good evening, sir.
What room is Mr. Fastbucks'?
[FASTBUCKS]
Oh, it's you.
Hmm, don't tell me
you've got new evidence
that I'm the man you want.
No, I'm not here for
that, Mr. Fastbucks.
I wanna know how
you win at roulette.
Well, it's commendable that
you're interested in
other things besides racing.
I also have a wide
range of interests.
After all, you never know
what kind of knowledge
may come in handy.
[chuckles]
[SPEED]
We haven't formally met,
so let me introduce myself. I--
It's not necessary.
One of my interests
is car racing,
so I know all about you, Speed.
I know you're one of the
youngest and fastest drivers
in the sport, and your car
is known as the Mach 5.
I have a theory about
the race tomorrow.
I think your knowledge of
roulette could be a great help.
[FASTBUCKS chuckles]
[FASTBUCKS] I congratulate you
on your perception, Speed.
In a way, racing is similar
to playing roulette.
There are certain
identical elements.
And you, being a highly
competitive young man,
want to know almost
too much in order to win.
I'm right, aren't I?
In winning at roulette
as well as car racing,
you must study all of
the elements involved:
Your competitors,
the conditions of the machines--
theirs as well as your own--
the velocity of the wind,
the weather itself,
and the atmosphere.
And most important of all,
you must know
your own condition.
Do you feel sharp? Alert?
And do you feel lucky?
The element of luck
can never be overlooked.
Perhaps it plays the most
important part of all.
And often, when you
feel lucky, you are lucky.
I guess you must make a lot
of calculations at the scene.
[FASTBUCKS]
I do.
But how are you able to figure
all those elements so fast?
It would take a genius!
My IQ is the highest possible.
I'm the smartest man
in the world.
[FASTBUCKS laughs]
There isn't a fact
that I don't remember.
I never know
what'll come in handy.
They say that
knowledge is power.
And if that's so,
I already have great power.
[grunts]
[FASTBUCKS] There is nothing
that I can lose at,
nothing at all!
Never!
And woe be to anyone
who gets in my way.
--[laughs]
--[phone rings]
[FASTBUCKS]
Yes?
That much?
Too bad, but the answer is no.
One of the men playing roulette,
he's lost a lot of money
and wanted to know
if I would lend him some,
so that he could try
to win back what he lost.
But why should I?
It's his hard luck.
Some men are stupid
enough to compete
without full knowledge
of what they're doing.
Ah, it's warm in here.
I hope you won't mind
if I remove my jacket.
Ah, there, that's better.
[groans]
Your right arm! It's wounded!
[FASTBUCKS gasps]
Yes, of course, it is.
And I'm the man that you
drove back to Monte Carlo.
Yes, I'm the one
that the police want.
I was lying earlier.
I robbed the bank up north
and needed you
to drive me back here.
That was only one of
my many criminal jobs.
Yes, I'm wanted by the police
in at least half
a dozen countries,
and I'm near the top
of the Interpol list.
I'm wanted for robbery,
murder, swindling,
and cheating at dominos.
I robbed that bank yesterday
because I needed
some pocket money.
[SPEED grunts]
[FASTBUCKS groans]
One thing you didn't figure
was how far I can kick my foot!
[FASTBUCKS] Oh, by the way,
Speed, I forgot to mention
how good I am at cards!
[SPEED gasps]
And I'm a pretty good fighter,
as you've just learned.
[SPEED groaning]
You haven't given up yet?
Well, let me warn you
that in judo,
I'm 2nd degree black belt.
All right, let's fight.
You're going to be sorry
that you found me, Speed.
[yells]
[SPEED gasps]
Sorry to have to do this.
[FASTBUCKS]
I ought to warn you that
I am also 3rd degree
black belt in karate!
But you're going to find that
out for yourself the hard way!
[yells]
[yelps]
[BOTH grunting]
[FASTBUCKS chuckles]
[BOTH grunt, groan]
[chuckles]
[SPEED gasps]
You're a very talented fighter.
But you know
nothing about fencing.
[SPEED gasping]
[FASTBUCKS]
And now...!
That trick won't work!
[SPEED grunting]
[cuckoo clock tweeting]
[buzzing]
[SPEED gasps]
They're down there, too!
There's no way out!
--[THUG A] There he is!
--[SPEED gasps]
[THUG A]
Fire!
[SPEED groaning]
There he is!
[SPEED gasps]
That way!
[SPEED] Come on, come on!
What's taking it so long?!
[panting]
[SPEED] Oh! It'll never
get here in time!
[footsteps]
[WOMAN B] But I never ordered
that from room service!
[WOMAN B yelping]
[WOMAN B screams]
[SPEED gasps]
[gasps]
[SPEED yells]
--[PEOPLE screaming]
--[sirens wailing]
Inspector Dubious?
This is Speed Racer.
I'm calling to warn you that
Mr. Fastbucks definitely
is the criminal
who stopped my car
up in the alps,
and he's at the hotel in
Monte Carlo right now. He--
Hello, Speed? Speed!
What's happening?! Hello!
[sirens wailing]
[POLICE A]
Open this door!
[grunts]
[POLICE A]
There's no one here!
[POLICE B]
He's gone!
I wonder where Speed is.
The Monte Carlo Grand Prix's
gonna start soon,
and unless he hurries
and gets here,
he's liable to miss it.
It's not like him to be so late.
I wish Sparky was here, too.
I can't check the Mach 5 myself.
After all, I'm not a mechanic.
I guess Sparky's mad because
he wanted to be the navigator,
but you took that job, instead.
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
Oh, I can't help wondering
if Speed's all right.
I hope he gets here soon.
[SPEED gasps]
[FASTBUCKS laughs]
You're getting worried
about the time for the race.
It's supposed to start
very soon, after all.
But don't worry, Speed,
the race is going
to be cancelled.
Cancelled?!
[FASTBUCKS] They're going
to televise the whole thing,
so let's watch it together, huh?
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Monte Carlo Grand Prix
is scheduled to start
in a few minutes.
And of all the cars which
qualified in the rally,
only the driver of
the Mach 5, Speed Racer,
has failed to show up here.
Unless he appears soon,
he'll miss out on the race!
One of the unusual features
of this dangerous race
is that only a limited
amount of gasoline
will be supplied to each car.
And they must complete
the race before
that supply of gasoline
is completely exhausted.
It's 8:30 on the dot.
Everything's right on schedule.
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies and
gentlemen, a catastrophe!
The gasoline tanks supplying
fuel to the racing cars
have just blown up!
[PEOPLE gasp, scream]
[BOTH scream]
Trixie and Spritle!
[FASTBUCKS cackling]
You're responsible for that!
You're right,
but it was only a test.
A car won't run
without any gasoline.
And what do you think if
all the gasoline in the world
was destroyed?
Airplanes, cars, buses, and
trucks wouldn't be able to run.
Only trains, that's all.
And if all my money
is invested in train stock,
I'll become a billionaire.
So all I have to do is destroy
all the oil refineries
in the world.
There are 293 in America,
64 in the Soviet Union,
17 in England. In fact, a total
of 640 throughout the world.
You saw how easy it was for me
to blow up those
tanks at the race.
Well, I can destroy
all the oil refineries
--in the world that way.
--You wouldn't dare!
Ah, but it's all arranged.
They're all scheduled
to be set off at noon today.
Can you imagine the confusion?
These machines can cause
electric short circuits
anywhere in the world.
And short circuits lead
to fire and explosion.
You are the most
dangerous man I've ever met.
And you're whacky.
No, I'm not whacky!
I'm a genius!
And I'm about to become
the richest man on Earth!
Unfortunately,
you know too much,
so I'm going to have to get
rid of you permanently.
I have just the method,
so stay right there.
I'll get back to you later!
[laughs]
[SPEED gasps]
[groans]
[gasping]
[TRIXIE] It was lucky
that no one was hurt!
[SPARKY] Yeah, and that
the race has been delayed.
I wonder where Speed is.
He must've heard
by now what happened,
and I'm sure he'd
get here if he could.
He might've gotten
into trouble, don't you think?
Wait a minute, that Mr.
Fastbucks got into the Mach 5
up in the alps soon after
he robbed a bank in France!
And so I suspect
that he's got a hideout
somewhere up on those mountains!
[TRIXIE]
I'll bet you're right!
And I think Speed could be
his prisoner up there!
What're we waiting for?
Let's go!
Be careful up ahead.
The road may be slippery,
but you mustn't use your brake.
[TRIXIE] You make a groovy
navigator, Sparky.
[SPARKY]
I know!
Get ready to make a right turn,
and immediately after that,
make a wide left.
[TRIXIE] This is near
where we met Mr. Fastbucks!
[BOTH gasp]
[FASTBUCKS cackling]
I know how smart you are.
So I figured that sooner
or later, you'd find me.
You're just in time to witness
the most spectacular show
the world has ever seen.
I'm going to blow up every
oil refinery on Earth!
But you probably
wouldn't enjoy it
unless your pal Speed
watches it with you.
Very well.
[TRIXIE gasps]
Speed! Has he been hurt?
I don't know. Let's find out.
Fire!
[SPEED gasps]
You're all here!
[SPRITLE] We've got
to help them, Chim Chim.
[FASTBUCKS]
I want that kid and the monkey
to get out of the trunk.
[BOTH scream]
He knows we're in here;
The jig's up!
Let's go!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[THUG B yelps]
[gunshots]
[FASTBUCKS gasps]
[FASTBUCKS groans]
That hurt!
Stop that monkey!
[THUG C grunts, groans]
[SPARKY yelps]
[SPARKY]
Hiya...
[SPRITLE gasping]
[SPRITLE screams]
[SPEED gasps]
I'm... free!
Good luck!
[TRIXIE gasps]
[SPEED grunting]
[THUGS groan]
[FASTBUCKS] Nice monkey.
Now come on, give me that bomb.
You're such a sweet,
little monkey.
You don't want a bomb.
Please give it to me.
[CHIM CHIM gulps]
[FASTBUCKS gasps]
[THUG D screams]
Trixie, our only chance is to
get out of here fast! Let's go!
Sparky, Spritle,
Chim Chim! Come on!
[SPRITLE]
Coming!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[SPEED]
Get in with us, Chim Chim!
They won't get far.
Little do they know that the
monkey has a bomb in its mouth,
and it will go off
in one minute.
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
Chim Chim! Throw that
bomb out of the car!
[FASTBUCKS chuckles]
There's going to be an
explosion... in 15 seconds.
[chuckles]
Six more seconds...
5... 4... 3... 2... 1...
[FASTBUCKS screams]
[SPRITLE]
That was close!
[SPARKY]
Too close!
Pow! It went up like a rocket!
You know, I'm glad they're
runnin' the rally over again.
Well, this time,
you're the navigator,
and you'd better do a good job.
Don't worry, I will!
--[DUBIOUS] Speed.
--[SPEED] Oh, hello, Inspector.
Thank you, Speed.
That criminal got
what he deserved.
Mach 5, get ready to start!
[TRIXIE]
Wait!
Get out, Sparky!
[SPARKY]
Huh?!
The car's gotta have
the same navigator as before.
That's what the rules say. Look.
Go!
I never heard of
that rule before.
I wonder if she coulda
been pullin' my leg.
Hey, come back here, Trixie!
That wasn't fair!
There's no such rule!
That's right, I made it up.
Goodbye, Sparky!
[NARRATOR] See the next exciting
episode of... Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪