♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR] This is the exotic
and mysterious city of Ambrocia,
located high in the Mystic
Mountains on Lake Ripplelaps.
[NARRATOR] Here, one of
the world's most famous races,
the Mystic Grand Prix,
is about to take place.
The famous Piston Powers is
in starting position number 1.
Also competing in the race
is another well-known driver,
the mysterious Racer X.
And driving his powerful
Mach 5 is Speed Racer.
[engines revving]
It's going to be
a dangerous race.
I hope Speed'll be careful.
He has a good chance of winning
in the supercharged Formula 1,
that new car Pops designed.
[NARRATOR] As the racers
rev up their engines
for the Mystic Grand Prix,
Prince Snowier and Princess
Gracious enter the royal box.
Princess Gracious
is going to wave the flag
signaling the start of the race.
She's lined up in my sights;
I'm ready to fire.
[RADIO VOICE] The noise those
cars will make as they go
will cover the
sound of the shot.
So nobody'll know
which direction
the bullet was fired from.
Get ready.
And don't miss.
[engines revving]
[CROWD gasps]
[gasps]
[PEOPLE murmuring]
There he is!
[tires screech]
[ASSASSIN groans]
[SPEED grunts]
[BOTH groaning, grunting]
[ASSASSIN yelps, screams]
[sirens wail]
[POLICE A]
Ladies and gentlemen,
because an attempt was just made
on the life of
Princess Gracious,
the police are looking for
the man who fired the rifle.
You will all be
questioned and searched.
[PEOPLE murmuring]
The man was found.
Speed Racer fought with him
and he fell off the roof.
We can let everybody go.
[POLICE B]
Okay, the search is over!
[snickers]
[knocking]
Customs. [chuckles]
[ALL snicker]
[grunts]
Something unexpected happened,
and our plan didn't work.
We failed to assassinate
Princess Gracious.
True, the plan didn't work,
but somebody stopped it.
[VILLAIN A]
Hm?!
What do ya mean?
Take a look at this.
I picked the
mirror up, gentlemen.
It was by the starting line.
Somebody used it to flash
light into our agent's eyes.
This means only one thing--
One of the racers
is a secret agent
of the International Police,
and they must've
found out about our plot.
He waited, then he
used the mirror.
We must find out who he is.
You're right!
Are you ready?
Run that film!
We'll take a good look
at all of the racers
taking part in
the Mystic Grand Prix.
This is Barecat Stunts,
the famous racer
who came here from
the country of Pomping.
He's been a professional
racer for 15 years.
Tailgate Jones in the
country of South Marsiponia.
[train whistles]
Our computer says these three
are likely suspects
of being a secret agent.
If one of them
is a secret agent,
then let's play it safe
and get rid of them all.
I've been studying the pictures
and I know their names by heart.
This is Rusty Muffle,
a fast man on curves.
Tailgate Crumple,
who's prone to accidents.
And Speed Racer,
who drives the Mach 5.
[MAN]
Okay, swing her out.
Careful, hold her steady now.
Okay, now lower it
onto the truck.
[TRIXIE gasps]
They almost dropped
the supercharged Formula 1.
And that would've been terrible!
I know, Pops put so much work
into designing and building
the supercharged Formula 1,
I wouldn't want anything
to happen to it.
Lower away!
Okay, that's perfect!
[SPEED grunts]
Thanks.
The supercharged Formula 1's
a wonderful car, Trixie.
And one of the best
features about it
is that there's no room for
Spritle and Chim Chim
in the trunk. Look.
Huh?!
We have plenty of room.
We even have
enough room for food
to last us for more
than a month, Speed.
[SPEED]
I give up.
Well, Sparky,
take good care of that car.
I will!
Don't worry about it.
See ya in Abalonia!
[NARRATOR] Speed and Trixie
leave the city of Ambrocia,
where the race was cancelled
when the assassination attempt
was made on the life
of Princess Gracious.
They head for Abalonia,
where the next race,
the hazardous Twist
'n' Turn, will be run.
Hello there, Mr. Muffle.
I'm sorry the Grand Prix
was cancelled.
[SPEED]
So am I.
Sir? I'd like you
to meet Trixie.
This is Mr. Muffle.
[TRIXIE]
Hello!
Hello, Trixie.
Call me Rusty. That's what
all my friends call me.
We're on our way to the
Twist 'n' Turn Race in Abalonia.
Will you be in it?
Yes, but I don't have much
chance; I'm new at racing.
[SPEED]
Well, good luck anyway.
[TRIXIE]
See ya later!
That's funny.
He said he's new at racing,
but he isn't young enough
to be a beginner.
You're right, Trixie.
I wonder what he did before
he decided to be
a professional racer.
He looks as if he might be
a pretty good driver.
Yes, but maybe he's only
pretending to be a professional.
[TRIXIE] Well, I hope we
find out eventually.
This is Matsy Hattie.
Muffle's car
just passed Point A.
[MATSY]
Now approaching Point B!
Roger and out.
This is Rusty Muffle?
Became a professional
racer only this year!
That means he could secretly
be the secret agent.
[ASSASSIN B]
I'll get rid of him.
--[tires screech]
--[MUFFLE gasps]
[MATSY] Speed Racer's car
just passed Point A.
It's on its way to Point B.
Speed Racer.
He drives a
specially-equipped car,
and he secretly could
be a secret agent.
Okay! Get ready.
--[knocking]
--[SPRITLE] Stop the car, Speed!
We've got to stretch our legs!
[TRIXIE]
Huh?!
Oh, look, Speed. Aren't those
mountains beautiful?
[SPEED]
They sure are.
Abalonia's a lovely country.
[SPEED yawns]
And Spritle's right; we needed
to stretch our legs.
Oh, Speed! Come here quick!
Look down there!
[SPEED]
What is it, Trixie?
[TRIXIE]
Look!
That's Mr. Muffle's car!
That's bad.
They found the other car
and they'll get wise to us.
There's something
very suspicious
about this whole thing.
Come on, Trixie.
We'd better call the police.
This looks deliberate to me.
[BOTH gasp]
[ASSASSIN LEADER]
Hold it right there.
[SPRITLE gasps]
Speed's in trouble!
--{SPRITLE] Speed!
--[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
Don't come down here! Keep away!
[SPRITLE]
Speed!
[SPRITLE grunting]
[SPRITLE]
Let go! Let go!
[laughs]
--[SPRITLE grunting]
--[CHIM CHIM gibbering]
[SPRITLE]
Let go!
Let me go! Put me down!
Who are you people anyway?
You must be the ones who caused
Mr. Muffle's car to be wrecked!
You're right.
Get rid of them, men!
--[TRIXIE gasps]
--[SPEED] Trixie!
[engine revving]
Huh?!
[ASSASSINS gasp]
It's Racer X!
--[SPEED, TRIXIE grunt]
--[ASSASSINS groan]
[yelps]
[SPRITLE, CHIM CHIM laugh]
--[SPEED, TRIXIE grunt]
--[ASSASSINS groan]
Let's get out of here!
Speed. I got here just in time.
Those men tried to
get rid of you because
they thought you might be
a secret agent, Speed.
Me, a secret agent?
Why, that's ridiculous!
[RACER X] Anyway,
they'll try to get you again,
so from now on,
you've gotta be extra careful.
See you around.
Where're you going?
I plan to do
a little sightseeing
before I join you in
the Twist 'n' Turn Race.
Where're you going?
If you must know, to Paris.
--[SECRETARY] Chief!
--[CHIEF] Hmm?
A report and
instructions just came
from International Police
branch in Abalonia.
They want us to keep an eye on
Rudolph Elegantor
and his organization.
And Number 9's coming to Paris.
That's good to hear.
Put me in touch with Number 8.
[SECRETARY]
Yes, sir.
[buzzing]
Number 8 is ready, sir.
Number 8, it's imperative
you keep a close eye
on Rudolph Elegantor.
[AGENT 8] Rudolph Elegantor
just left his hotel
and is headed somewhere.
Okay, don't lose him.
Follow him everywhere.
[AGENT 8]
Yes, sir.
--[gunfire]
--[AGENT 8 yelps, groans]
Number 8, what's up?
Number 8, what's up?!
[ELEGANTOR chuckles]
Hello there, Chief.
Who is that speaking?
[ELEGANTOR]
Rudolph Elegantor.
Forget about Number 8; you won't
be talking to him ever again!
[ELEGANTOR] Number 8 had an
unfortunate little accident,
which is too bad because he
was one of your best agents
in the International
Secret Service.
[chuckles]
Take me to the nearest
railroad station.
[ELEGANTOR] Ahh, gentlemen,
we got rid of Rusty Muffler
and Tailgate Crumple,
but we failed to get Speed.
Uh-oh!
Speed's got to be a secret
agent, but that won't stop us.
We'll drop Operation A
and do Operation B,
which means that we failed
to take over Ambrocia,
so we'll concentrate on
taking over Abalonia.
Fine, I'll be just as happy
takin' over the
country of Abalonia.
It should be easy,
because in a few days,
they're holding
the Twist 'n' Turn Race there!
That'll give us the perfect
opportunity to take over.
Once we get rid of
a certain knight in our way,
it will be checkmate!
Abalonia's city looks so modern!
And it took them only
ten years to build it.
It's hard to believe that
this used to be such
a backward country,
but President Montebank
has done wonders!
He's a great man!
So in a few days, the city will
be holding its 10th anniversary!
And to celebrate,
they're holding the big race.
Right! I'm gonna win it and
get the President's trophy!
[TRIXIE] Oh, Speed!
What an elegant hotel!
[TRIXIE sighs]
[SPEED]
Mm-hmm!
[BELLBOY]
I'll take your bag, sir.
It must be in the trunk.
--[SPEED] Uh, no, no--
--[BELLBOY gasps]
Here ya are!
May I have the keys
so I can park your car?
[SPEED]
Oh, sure. Here.
[chuckles]
Hello, Speed! We heard
you ran into some trouble
along the road from Ambrocia,
but weren't hurt.
That's right.
I was lucky,
but Tailgate Crumple
and Rusty Muffle weren't.
They crashed off the road
and were goners!
Hey, where's Racer X?
[REPORTER]
We haven't seen him.
I figure he still
hasn't reached Abalonia.
[SPEED]
Oh, I guess not. See ya!
[SPEED] Racer X said those
mysterious men
tried to get rid of me
because they thought
I might be a secret agent.
I wonder what he meant.
And where is he?
Chief, Number 9 is here
to give you a report.
[CHIEF]
Hmm?
Hello, 9.
Chief, I've got bad news.
As you know,
they got rid of Number 8
and one of the other racers,
and made an attempt on still
a third racer's life.
We've gotta do something quickly
before more innocent
people are involved.
[CHIEF]
Mm-hmm!
Where's Elegantor's gang now?
What're they up to?
They took care of our man
who was following them,
so we have no idea
where they are right now
or just what they
may be planning.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
back at the hotel in Abalonia.
--[CHIM CHIM gibbering]
--[SPRITLE] Mm-mmm!
--[TRIXIE] Uh-oh!
--[knocking]
[SPEED]
Hello.
[HOTEL MANAGER] Mr. Racer,
you and Trixie are invited
to come at 6:00 tonight
to President Montebank's home.
Thank you very much.
It's a great honor
and we'll be happy to come.
Tell the President
we'll be there at six.
[SPEED]
Hurry, Trixie!
But what'll I wear?
I don't have a thing
to wear tonight.
Hooray! Hooray!
Speed and I were invited.
You'll have to stay right here.
And that's final!
[SPRITLE]
Okay, Chim Chim.
The usual plan:
Into the trunk, okay?
This is Speed Racer,
please bring my car
to the front of the hotel.
[SPEED]
Thanks.
We'll be back later.
[BOTH panting]
[SPRITLE gasps]
They're gone, Chim Chim!
They left us behind!
[THUG] They left and they
didn't check the tires.
They don't suspect that we
fixed it so the car'll crash.
That, in two or three minutes,
the left front tire
is gonna get too hot
and then it'll blow up.
You fixed the tire
so it'll blow up?!
Huh?! You weren't
supposed to hear that!
[CHIM CHIM gibbering]
[THUG]
Come back!
Come back here!
--[knocking]
--[THUG] Open this door!
[THUG]
Let me in! Open up!
[SPRITLE] Chim Chim,
we've got to do something.
We've got to warn Speed,
but how can we do it?
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[gasps]
Trixie's transmitter!
A great idea!
I'll try it if I can find it!
[THUG]
Open this door!
Open it or I'll smash it open!
Open up!
[SPRITLE]
I think I see the transmitter!
[beeping]
Spritle, what're you doing
with Trixie's transmitter?
[SPRITLE] Speed,
you're in terrible danger!
They fixed your front left tire.
It'll blow up and you'll crash!
The left front tire?!
[SPRITLE] Yes! When it gets
too hot, it'll blow up!
[gasps]
[SPEED panting]
[TRIXIE gasps]
--[SPEED] Get down!
--[TRIXIE gasps]
--[knocking]
--[THUG] Open this door!
[SPRITLE]
Speed! Help me!
[BOTH gasp]
[THUG grunting]
[SPRITLE]
Speed! Help!
[THUG yelping, groaning]
[yelping continues]
Chim Chim,
I'm out of ammunition.
[THUG grunts, groans]
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[THUG]
Now I'll getcha!
I'll fix you... I'll--
[SPRITLE]
Speed!
I knew you'd get here in time!
[THUG screams]
I thought you'd be
outta the way by now!
Thanks to Spritle's
warning, I'm not.
Ugh, thanks to what happens at
the President's house tonight,
the whole country'll be ours.
[SPEED]
Huh?!
[THUG]
You heard me!
At 6:15, the President'll make
a speech welcoming you racers.
A time bomb has been attached
to the microphone,
set to go off at exactly 6:15.
Get me President Montebank's
house right away,
and please hurry!
[THUG]
You're wasting your time.
We cut the telephone line.
You won't be able to warn them.
[SPEED]
Is that so?!
[THUG groans]
Only three more minutes
and that bomb goes off.
You'll never make it there!
[sirens wail]
[ticking]
[RACER X]
I wonder where Speed is.
He's late.
[MAN B]
Ladies and gentlemen,
President Montebank wishes to
make a speech welcoming you.
[tires screech]
[applause]
[GUARD]
Hey! Your identification card!
[groans]
[applause]
[ticking]
[SPEED]
Halt!
Who are you? What do you want?
[MAN C]
Stop! [grunts]
[groans]
[SPEED]
Get out of the way!
[NARRATOR]
See the next
thrilling episode
of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪