♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
They're after us!
[SPEED]
Huh?!
[NARRATOR]
The mysterious Mammoth Car
challenges Speed Racer,
driving the Mach 5,
in the No Limit World Race.
[TRIXIE gasps]
[NARRATOR] Using one of the
ingenious devices on the Mach 5,
Speed tries to make a
shortcut through the forest.
[NARRATOR] But the Mammoth
Car is able to follow.
Speed tries a desperate move
to slash one of the
Mammoth Car's tires.
[NARRATOR] Earlier,
50 million dollars in gold
was stolen from
the National Bank.
The police suspect it is
somewhere inside
the Mammoth Car,
and is being smuggled
out of the country.
Now, Cruncher Block, the
owner of the Mammoth Car,
must see that
Speed Racer and Trixie
do not learn the secret of
the car and where it's headed.
Hang on!
[BOTH scream]
[DRIVER A]
That does it.
Let's go!
Mammoth Car,
calling Cruncher Block.
Mammoth Car, calling Cruncher!
We just sent the Mach 5 to
the bottom of Lake Icy Chill.
According to the telescanner,
the Mammoth Car is gone.
Now it'll be safe to get
out of here. Here we go!
This is Trixie in the Mach 5,
calling Inspector Detector.
Speed and I have found out the
Mammoth Car is not just a racer,
it's loaded with men with guns!
And they're trying to stop us
from finding out some very
important secret about the car!
We'll continue in the
race as long as we can,
but please investigate the
Mammoth Car as soon as possible.
[SPEED] We think it might be
carrying the 50 million dollars
in gold bars stolen
from the National Bank!
Can't think of anything
else to add, can you?
[SPEED]
We've told him all we know.
We'll use our homing robot
to send the information
to the Inspector.
[TRIXIE]
Mm!
It's important.
I hope it makes it.
[NARRATOR] Cruncher Block,
owner of the Mammoth Car,
is flying above the road
being used for the race.
Hey, look at that, Boss.
[CRUNCHER] I know the scenery's
gorgeous, who cares?
[MAN A] But I'm not
lookin' at the scenery,
I'm lookin' at the Mach 5.
You're dreaming!
That's no dream,
it's a nightmare!
I thought they got rid of it.
They did, but something
must'a gone wrong
because that's the
Mach 5, all right!
Let's look closer.
[MAN A]
Mm-hm!
[BOTH scream]
That pilot better learn to fly!
I think they did it on purpose!
I wanna talk to the Mammoth Car.
Listen, you stoneheads!
I gave you orders to get
rid of those two nosy kids.
Can't ya do even a
cinch job like that?
What went wrong with it?
Nothin'! We knocked
them into the lake;
that's where they are!
[CRUNCHER]
Oh yeah?!
Look behind ya! And don't
you tell me they're ghosts!
[DRIVER A]
Huh?!
Ah!
The Mach 5!
[DRIVER B]
Ahh!
It's them all right!
But how'd they get
outta that lake?!
[growls] Now listen carefully.
The Mammoth Car will be stopping
at the fueling point any minute.
Our men are waiting
there for you,
and they'll refuel your car,
but they'll also take
care of the Mach 5.
So make sure that
it follows ya there!
They're liable to
learn our secret--
[CRUNCHER]
Do as I say!
[BOTH scream]
I wonder where the
Mammoth Car's headed!
If we follow them, maybe we can
find out what they're up to!
[NARRATOR] Unknown to Speed,
this is his older brother, Rex,
who ran away from
home years ago.
[SPEED]
Hm...
I don't see anybody here;
it seems deserted.
[TRIXIE]
Uh-huh.
That plane!
[SPEED] Well that's funny...
Let's take a look.
[gasps]
[SPEED]
Get down!
Hold your fire!
They're trapped in there!
Let her roll!
[BOTH gasp]
[NARRATOR] No one knows that
Speed's younger brother,
Spritle, and his pal, Chim Chim,
were stowaways on the plane.
Don't make a sound, Chim Chim!
We don't want them
to know we're here.
Hey!
Those men are gonna do something
bad to Speed and Trixie.
I've got to help my brother!
[CHIM CHIM growls]
[gasps]
[gunshot]
[BOTH scream]
[SPRITLE]
Run, Chim Chim!
[SPRITLE gasps]
Look, Trixie, this must
be the secret place
where they refuel
the Mammoth Car!
[TRIXIE] Mm-hm! What do you
plan to do with both of us?
[CRUNCHER]
I'll tell ya.
I'm finished with this
secret headquarters,
so I'm gonna get rid of it and
the two of you while I'm at it.
And it'll be more interesting
than just knocking ya
into Lake Icy Chill.
What do ya think is in that
crate that you're tied to?
Three tons of dynamite.
[gasps]
[CRUNCHER]
The fuse is gonna be lit.
And then that
trolley car you're on
will be pushed
down into the mine.
[CRUNCHER chuckles]
Somewhere deep in that tunnel,
a fuse is gonna
set off the dynamite
and that'll be the
end of both of you.
Then nobody'll learn what you
found out about my Mammoth Car.
Too bad you have to lose the
race and everything else.
[laughing]
[DRIVER C]
I'm ready...
Cut it!
[RACER X]
No you don't!
Let go!
[yelps]
Well, we must be on our way
to finish the race. Have fun.
Now! Light the fuse!
[gasps]
[SPRITLE]
Jump!
[SPEED]
Oh! It's you!
[SPRITLE screams]
[TRIXIE gasps]
[screams]
[ALL gasp]
[RACER X]
You just avoided that crash.
The dynamite won't hurt you now.
It's Racer X!
Thank you for switching those
rails in the nick of time!
You saved us.
If I hadn't arrived, you
would've been blown up.
Those men'll do anything to win.
How did you know where you
could find us, Racer X?
You always seem to arrive just
when we need you the most.
[SPEED]
There's something about him
that reminds me
of Rex, my brother.
Can something be the matter?
You're looking at me in
a very strange way, Speed.
Tell me! What's on your mind?
[SPEED]
Nothing!
[SPRITLE]
Those bad men!
They were about to
smash the Mach 5.
I hope you'll never
again leave your car
while in the middle of a race.
Hurry! You may be able to
catch up to the Mammoth Car.
Thanks for everything, Racer X!
Now we should have
no more trouble.
[DRIVER B] This is the Mammoth
Car, calling Cruncher Block.
Did you get rid of those kids?
We're running right on schedule.
[CRUNCHER]
Good, we'll meet ya at the boat.
[NARRATOR] Speed and Trixie
race all night in the Mach 5.
Morning!
It looks as if it's
gonna be a groovy day!
[NARRATOR]
At the checkpoint,
Inspector Detector and
Speed's father, Pops,
are waiting anxiously.
[ANNOUNCER] This is the first
car to reach the checkpoint.
So far, the Mammoth
Car is winning.
Well, of course we are.
And we're gonna
win the whole race.
Now stamp the certificate with
the time that we reached here.
[OFFICIAL A]
There you are.
That gives the exact
time to the second.
Okay, you can continue the race.
[INSPECTOR]
Hold it!
--[DRIVER A] The police...
--[DRIVER B] What do they want?!
We think you might be smuggling.
We want to inspect the car.
[DRIVER A]
Again...?
You did already!
[DRIVER B] We got nothing
to hide, so look around!
Don't miss a thing!
Inspect everything carefully!
--Go ahead!
--[POLICEMEN] Yes, sir!
[DRIVER B gasps]
[DRIVER B]
Speed Racer and the Mach 5!
[DRIVER A]
What?
I thought he was out of the way!
Speed Racer!
Glad to see you!
Inspector, you'd better make
a thorough investigation
of the Mammoth Car!
[INSPECTOR]
We will!
We got the message by the
homing robot that you sent
tellin' us about that big car!
I didn't know you'd
be here, Pops!
We've got Spritle and
Chim Chim with us in the Mach 5!
[POPS]
Huh?! You do?!
I don't see them. Where are
the little rascals, huh?
They're both in
the trunk in back.
Huh? No, they're not.
There's nobody back here, Speed.
[DRIVER B]
Clear the road!
The big car's leaving.
[POLICEMEN yelp]
[SPEED]
Spritle!
[SPRITLE]
Come on, Chim Chim, get in!
[gasps]
Stop that car!
[INSPECTOR]
Halt!
[growls]
[SPEED] Hang on, Trixie!
We're going after it!
[TRIXIE]
Okay, hurry, Speed!
[SPRITLE]
Hey, that's funny. It's empty.
There's nothing in
the Mammoth Car!
[SPRITLE gasps]
[chuckles]
We'll be able to
catch them, Trixie.
[TRIXIE]
Oh, good!
In a few minutes,
we'll be at the boat.
[DRIVER A]
Mm-hm!
[INSPECTOR] They're getting
close to the finishing line.
[POPS] Then they won't
be able to go any further,
and you can arrest 'em!
[ANNOUNCER] As they come
into the homestretch,
the Mammoth Car and the Mach 5
are tied for first place.
Only a few more seconds,
and the great No Limit World
Race will be all over!
Here they come to
the finishing line!
And as they cross
it in a dead heat,
it's an absolute tie
for first place!
[CROWD cheering]
It may be the momentum
from the speed at which both
cars have been racing,
but they haven't slowed down!
The Mammoth Car is
even going faster!
Let us down!
We won't do anything!
Cut the rope!
Please, let us down!
[DRIVER C]
You'll behave yourselves?
[SPRITLE] We won't do anything
we shouldn't, I promise.
[DRIVER C]
Yeah, okay then.
We had to do that,
so I kept my word.
Hi-- Uh!
[screams]
Those two kids are
still with 'em!
Don't worry,
I'll give them a blast.
[CRUNCHER]
Yeah...
[BOTH scream]
What happened? Why didn't
it go on the boat, huh?!
[BOTH whimpering]
[SPRITLE]
That's the way!
Now keep the Mammoth
Car going straight,
and no monkey
business, understand?
Faster, faster!
[DRIVER B]
Who are you?
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[DRIVER B]
Monkey business, huh?!
[DRIVER B groans]
[DRIVER A screams]
Hey, how do we stop the car?
We've gotta find the
brakes and use them!
Hang on! I've gotta
reach the brakes
or we're going
to crash! Hang on!
Stop! Stop the car before
it crashes! Stop it!
Help! We're headed right
for that big oil tank!
There's something wrong
with the Mammoth Car;
it's going to crash
into that oil tank!
Help me, Speed!
You've gotta take
the wheel, Trixie!
[TRIXIE]
Huh?!
Spritle!
[SPRITLE] Ahh! Speed,
we're going to crash!
[SPEED]
Ah! Hang on!
It's gonna be the end
of my Mammoth Car!
[gasps]
[TRIXIE]
Speed! Oh, Speed!
So, that's it.
The gold was built right into
the Mammoth Car and painted.
[CRUNCHER]
My plan is ruined!
I could've gotten that stolen
gold out of the country,
but not now! Not now!
Be careful; it's
liable to explode!
[CRUNCHER] Oh...
My car... My golden car.
[BOTH laughing]
[INSPECTOR]
Congratulations, Speed.
You certainly ran a great race.
The Mammoth Car
was disqualified,
and so even though
the race was a tie,
the Mach 5's been
declared the winner.
You both did a great job!
And besides, you
found the stolen gold.
[SPRITLE]
Hmph!
Well, what's the matter?
Why are you both acting like
that? Is something wrong?
Some people get an award and
some people get nothing at all,
even though they deserve
a medal at least.
They're jealous.
But maybe if you give
them something, Inspector,
they won't be so hurt.
[INSPECTOR]
Mm-hm.
And both of you have
also done a very fine job.
Here, please accept this
small token of our gratitude.
Aw, is that all we get?
We were hoping for some candy.
[POPS, INSPECTOR laugh]
Why don't you put your hands in?
[BOTH]
Hm?
[SPRITLE gasps]
[ALL laughing]
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪