♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[SPEED] You are watching
the most advanced designed
and one of the fastest
racing cars in the world.
It's called the "Mach 5."
Watch it really go.
[SPEED] The Mach 5 is the
result of brilliant concept
and design and hard work.
It was built by
one of the geniuses
of the automotive
industry: my father.
And you're about to see
just how the fabulous
Mach 5 came to be.
But first, let me demonstrate
how well it handles.
[engine revs]
[ALL cheering]
[PIT CREW A]
Speed! What a race!
[PIT CREW B] What a race,
Speed! You were fantastic!
[SPEED chuckles] Thanks!
You had the race sewn up
by the second lap, Speed!
I've gotta hand it to you!
Someday, you'll be
champion of the world!
[PIT CREW D]
Nobody can beat you!
That was a great
race you ran, Speed!
You beat us fair and square!
You're the best driver
I've ever seen, Speed!
[SPEED]
Aw, thanks.
How would you like
to join my team
as a professional racer?
[SPEED]
Huh? I don't know...
Speed, you can race with
all of us in the Grand Prix.
I wish I could...
[SPEED] ...but Pops doesn't
want me to be a pro.
Ohh...
Your father's a top engineer
working for our company, Speed.
Maybe he'll change his mind
if we ask him, huh?
[SPEED]
I doubt it...
[PIT CREW A]
Speed, join us, huh?
[PIT CREW B]
We need you, Speed.
I wanna be a professional racer!
I wanna be the top champion!
I want that more than
anything in the world!
Hmm. You're a fast,
skillful driver, Speed,
and I do think you've
got a good chance
to realize your ambition.
Just stick to it.
Thanks, sir!
Don't worry about that.
You can't lose with this amazing
car! It can do everything!
It's a masterpiece
of your father's!
You should be proud
of him, Speed.
[SPEED]
Oh, I am!
But right now, he's working
on making it better
with an even faster engine
and all kinds of other parts.
It was true: Pops was going
to improve the Mach 5.
[POPS] This is the model of
the latest engine I've designed.
It will have more horsepower
than any other car engine
of its size.
Using the latest metals,
fuel, and ignition system,
I can succeed in boosting
the RPMs to 30,000.
[PRESIDENT]
Thirty thousand?!
If I didn't believe you,
I'd say it was unbelievable!
I've worked on it for a year. I
hope you will give the go-ahead
to actually build the engine
according to this plan here.
Don't waste time rebuilding it!
What?! You haven't heard the
rest of my plans for the Mach 5!
I've heard enough, Mr. Racer!
How can you be against it
when you haven't even heard
the rest of the plan
I worked on all year?!
I don't believe
the plans can work!
I'm a liar?!
Mr. Racer!
[POPS]
Is that what you're calling me?!
Oh! Sorry, sir...
[PRESIDENT] And you, Mr. Van
Ruffle, you'd better calm down!
But, Mr. President, I'm chief
engineer at this company!
I've been working on
engine designs for years;
I know what will work
and won't work,
and I say Mr. Racer's
designs won't work!
You're claiming
my engine won't work
before you've even
studied my design!
I don't have to study
the whole thing!
Your idea to redesign
the Mach 5 is pretty bad
because I don't think your car
was too hot to begin with!
You've gone about the whole
thing in the wrong way!
Mr. President, all I ask
is that you develop my plans
and give the car a try.
I can't do that without
the unanimous agreement
of this board.
If the car turns out
to be a failure,
do you think this company
should have to pay for
your incompetence, eh?!
So that's your
decision. All right.
You've had your chance,
and I'm not going to
ask you for another.
Glad to see you leave,
Mr. Racer. Good riddance!
[POPS]
I'll rebuild the Mach 5 myself
and I'll prove that
my design will work.
[VAN RUFFLE]
We'll see, we'll see!
Oh, we'll see...
[chuckles]
[SPEED] And so, Pops
quit his job that day,
and I drove him toward home.
Gee, Pops, maybe you shouldn't
have quit your factory job.
I wouldn't've if they'd
let me rebuild the car.
Why didn't they
give you the go ahead
after all the work
you put into the plans?
One of the board
members was jealous
and didn't even wanna
look at my designs,
and the board wouldn't give me
the go ahead, so I blew up.
I'm gonna forget about
driving on a team.
--What?!
--Nothing, Pops.
Maybe I'm wrong about
rebuilding the Mach 5.
Maybe it would be a failure...
And it also might turn out
to be the best racing car
in the world.
[POPS]
Hmm...
[BIKER A]
After 'em!
You boys trying to
take up the whole road?!
Hey! Come back here!
Come back! He took the plans!
Thanks for the plans, Pops!
Give them back to me!
You won't get away with them!
How can we stop them?
Pops, take the wheel.
[POPS]
No, Speed!
Now, give me those plans!
[BIKER A]
Let me go, we'll crash!
[SPEED]
Give them to me!
[BIKER A] What're you doing?!
I'll lose control!
[SPEED]
I want those plans back!
[BOTH grunting]
[BIKER A]
You take 'em!
Bye-bye, and thanks!
Come back here! Those plans
don't belong to you!
Hey! Stop!
Stop, or I'll stop you!
Hey!
[BIKER B]
Hey, I can't see, let go!
Take 'em!
[BIKER C]
Thanks, and so long!
Unhand me!
[gasps]
[BIKER C screaming]
[BIKER D]
Look out!
[BIKERS yelping]
Okay, now I'm gonna
give you a taste
of the medicine you deserve!
As former champion of the
Westside Grunters and Groaners,
I promise you're in
for a lot of groaning!
[BIKERS growl]
Uh-oh!
[BIKER F growling]
[BIKER F squealing]
He's even tougher than he talks!
[BIKER E]
Oh yeah?
[BIKER E yelping]
[SPEED]
Oh! It's Trixie!
Hey, Trixie, Trixie!
I'm down here!
[SPEED] Some motorcyclists
are racing up the road!
See if you can catch them!
[SPEED]
Pops' plans were stolen.
How could he've been
so careless, Speed?
[SPEED]
Trixie, hurry!
I'm going. I'll try
to find the men.
[laughing]
[POPS]
Ooh...
[BIKER G]
Huh?
--Hi.
--[BIKER G yelling]
[BIKER G screaming]
[squeals]
[yells]
That's the way, Speed!
You're a chip off the old block!
Show 'em they can't
fool with racers!
[groans]
[gasps]
[laughing]
[screaming]
[groaning]
Tell Pops next time he shouldn't
give those plans away so easily.
Don't worry, Trixie,
these plans for the Mach 5
are the most valuable
thing we've got.
To me, Speed's more valuable.
[POPS laughing]
Save some for me!
[CHIM CHIM babbles]
[POPS] Somebody tried
to steal the plans,
so that must mean
that they're valuable.
Don't you think so?
Yes, but now that
you've quit your job,
you won't know what
to do with yourself.
And I know how you
like to keep busy.
How about remodeling my kitchen,
rebuilding the garage,
and planting some shrubbery.
Hey, what a groovy idea, Pops!
And I'll help you
with everything!
Okay, but first, I'm gonna work
on remodeling the Mach 5 myself,
and prove to them at the
factory that it really works.
[POPS laughing]
But where will you get
the money for the parts you need
to rebuild the car?
[POPS]
Money... Hmm...
Of course, if you worked hard,
I'm sure you could
finish the job.
Sure, Pops,
don't be discouraged.
Well, I am! Where will I get
the money I'm gonna need?
[POPS groaning]
[music playing]
Quiet!
[SPRITLE crying]
Here, Spritle, here's
a whole new batch of cookies.
[SPRITLE giggles]
[crying]
[POPS]
Ohh... Driving me insane!
[VAN RUFFLE]
You stoneheads!
Don't tell me you're sorry!
[BIKER A] But we are
sorry, Mr. Van Ruffle.
Speed's strong, and
he got help from the sky
in the form of a helicopter.
What kind of excuse is that?!
It's ridiculous!
[MAN chuckles]
I figured those guys would
botch the job, and they did.
Gimme 5,000 clams,
and I'll get the plans.
You charge $5,000?!
You, sir, are kidding.
--[MAN] Oh no.
--Oh yeah?
[MAN]
Ace Ducey doesn't kid.
If you want those plans,
it'll cost you 5,000 clams.
If you don't want 'em,
forget it.
All right, it's a deal.
You'll have the plans
for the Mach 5.
[SPEED]
I won't be a professional racer.
Instead, I'll go to work
and earn enough money
so that Pops will be able
to rebuild the Mach 5.
[BOY humming]
Hiya, Sparky.
Oh, hi, Speed!
This is a groovy
heap, isn't it?
[SPEED]
Yeah.
The engine in there is a V8
with double overhead cam.
Hey, what's the matter? What're
you lookin' so sad about?
I'm selling my car...
[SPARKY]
Huh?! Selling the Mach 5?!
[SPEED]
Mm-hm.
Oh, come off it.
Your father's against you
becoming a professional racer,
but you don't have
to sell your car.
It's not that, Sparky,
it's just that I need the money.
You need money? Why don't you
tell me what this is all about?
I wanna give it to Pops so
he can build the super engine.
I get it, Speed, but they
told him at the factory
the engine wouldn't work.
I want Pops to build
the engine, Sparky.
I know how you feel, Speed,
but read this before
you do anything.
"A Trial Race across
Sword Mountain,
five thousand bucks
to the winner."
So why don't you enter it?
Pops would blow
a gasket if I did...
[SPARKY] But, Speed, wouldn't it
be worse if you sold the Mach 5?
You're right! I'll enter!
Now you're being smart, Speed,
but Sword Mountain's gonna
be a tough course to drive,
so I'll fix the Mach 5
for climbing mountains.
That'll be great! Thanks.
[POPS] You should knock
before you come in.
Who are you anyway?
My name's Ace Ducey.
And what do you want?
[ACE] Your designs for
rebuilding the Mach 5.
[POPS]
You can't have 'em.
[ACE]
Get over there.
I'm just gonna help myself.
Stay outta the way!
[POPS] You're not going
to get them, Mr. Ducey.
[ACE]
Oh, no? We'll see about that.
Where'd you hide those plans?
C'mon, where are they?
[SPEED]
Huh?
I'll be back to get what I want.
Who was that?
He came to get my plans
for rebuilding the Mach 5.
He carried a gun!
Oh, he did, huh?
[POPS] He's dangerous,
Speed! Let him go!
[POPS] Using invisible ink
and drawing the designs
on this windshield glass
was a brilliant idea.
Nobody'll think
of looking there!
[POPS chuckles]
[SPARKY]
Okay!
The Mach 5's all ready
for mountain racing, Speed!
Great! Now I wanna take
it out for a road test.
[SPARKY]
Go!
Wow, one minute and 34 seconds.
Great! Did you see that, Trixie?
He was really moving!
[SPEED]
Huh...? Ah...
Hey, that car
belongs to Duggery!
--[TRIXIE] Duggery!
--He races dirty!
What's he doing to him?
[gasps]
[yelping]
[SPRITLE, TRIXIE scream]
[tires screeching]
--[TRIXIE] Speed!
--[SPARKY] You okay, Speed?
Are you hurt?!
[SPRITLE]
Speedy. Talk to us, Speedy.
[SPARKY]
Hey, Speed.
[groaning]
[SPRITLE, SPARKY]
Speed!
[SPARKY]
What's the big idea, Duggery?!
Now Speed won't be able to enter
the Sword Mountain race!
Speed's going to be
a professional racer?
That's very interesting.
You told him.
Ooh! I forgot it was secret.
I would've beaten
you anyway, Speed,
so you're lucky you won't
be competing! So long!
You were planning to be
in a professional race?
Pops isn't gonna like it!
He's not supposed to know!
Don't tell him, Spritle!
He wants to win money so
Pops can build the new engine.
[TRIXIE]
Oh, I see.
I won't tell Pops, and
don't you either, Chim Chim!
[ALL laughing]
[SPEED sighs]
[SPARKY whistling]
[SPEED]
Put her on.
[SPARKY]
Okay!
There. Now the Mach 5 has
Pops' special grip tires system
for mountain areas.
How can you lose?
Uh-oh.
There's one thing missing;
there's no windshield!
Let's forget about it, Sparky.
I'll just have to race
without any glass on the car.
Don't be foolish, Speed,
you need the protection.
There isn't time
to go looking for it.
But it'll be dangerous
without glass.
Here's the windshield glass.
[SPEED]
Huh?
Nice goin', Spritle!
That's not my glass, though.
That belongs to Pops.
Don't worry about it, Speed.
We'll take care of Pops.
[phone rings]
[POPS]
Pops speaking.
[SPRITLE] Hi, Pops,
is it okay if Speed borrows
your windshield glass
for a little while?
[POPS]
Why does he want it?!
Where is Speed?! Huh?!
[SPRITLE] He's going to
race at Sword Mountain.
Ah! I shouldn't have
told Pops that.
[POPS]
He took my windshield, huh?!
I wonder what Pops
is so sore about?
[POPS] I've drawn
the designs in invisible ink
on that windshield, and now,
if the glass is broken,
those plans will
be gone forever.
Ah!
Clever of you to hide those
designs on that windshield.
It makes my job easier.
To get them, all I have
to do is take his car.
You'd better not!
[POPS grunts]
[ACE chuckles]
I'm going to win
this race, Speed,
and those 5,000 bucks
will be mine.
You'd better not count
on them, Duggery.
Get ready! It's about to start!
This is gonna be
some ride, Chim Chim.
[ANNOUNCER]
All drivers stand by.
When the flag is lowered,
all drivers will run
to their cars and start.
Racing positions on
the track will be determined
by quick starts and getaways.
Get ready.
The flag will be lowered
and the race will begin
in exactly 15 seconds.
[POPS grunting]
Call off the race?
Why should we do that?
Because if you don't,
there's going to be a disaster.
They'll do anything to
get my plans. Call it off!
[CROWD cheering]
[engine revs]
[tires squeal]
[POPS groaning]
Speed, watch out for Duggery!
[screams]
[CROWD shouting]
[gasps]
[ACE] Our target's car five.
We want its windshield.
The other cars are gonna be
in the way. Get rid of them!
[SPEED]
Huh?
I dunno who's driving
those new cars in the race,
but they're looking for trouble.
I don't want any of 'em
trying to wreck me.
Look, Chim Chim,
we're in for it! Ah!
You'd better do as I say,
otherwise, I'll smash you
right off the course!
All I want is your windshield
glass. Give it to me,
or I promise you'll never
reach the finish line!
[SPEED] There's only one
reason he wants the glass:
I'll bet Pops hid
the design on it.
C'mon, take it off if you can!
[ACE]
That fool of a kid.
[yelps]
[NARRATOR] Speed is in the most
desperate race of his life.
Will he finish it,
or will it finish him?
See the next episode
of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪