♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[SPEED]
The controls on the Mach 5--
the amazing car designed
and built by my father.
Control Button A:
releases powerful jacks
which boost the car so that
our mechanic, Sparky,
can make repairs
and adjustments.
Control B: When this
button is pressed,
the Mach 5 sprouts
special grip tires
for traction over
any kind of terrain.
Control C releases
powerful rotary saws
from the front of the car
to slice through any
and all obstacles.
D: When pressed, this button
releases a powerful deflector
which seals the cockpit into
a bullet and crash-proof
and watertight chamber.
E is the control for
special illumination,
which enables me to see
further and more clearly
than with ordinary headlights.
When I'm in a dangerous place,
I can traverse these lights
singly or in tandem.
F is the control I use when
the Mach 5 is underwater.
The cockpit is
supplied with oxygen,
and then a periscope is
raised to scan the surface.
Everything that it sees
is relayed down to me
by television.
Control G releases
a homing robot,
which can carry pictures
or tape-recorded messages
to whomever and wherever
I wanna send them.
With this car that Pops built,
the most fabulous
car ever driven,
I've been competing in auto
races throughout the world.
[engine revving]
I love taking the wheel!
[SPEED]
Take it easy, Trixie.
The speed limit through
here's only 80 miles an hour.
Huh? Oh!
I didn't realize we were
going twice that fast.
It drives so beautifully.
I know that.
But we've got to obey the law.
Huh?
Looks like a reckless
driver back there.
[gasps]
[whistles]
Watch where you're driving!
You drive just like a girl!
Did you hear that?!
[SPEED]
Forget it!
[BOY A] What's the matter?
We hurt your feelings?
[BOY B]
Wah, now we got her mad.
[SPEED]
Hey, take it easy.
[BOYS heckling]
--[TRIXIE gasps]
--[SPEED] Careful!
--[BOY A] Let's do it again!
--[BOY C] Hang on!
[BOYS laughing]
[SPEED]
Cut that out!
You want us to crash?!
[BOYS laughing]
[tires screech]
[SPEED]
Look out!
[BOTH gasp]
[tires screech]
[SPEED sighs]
We almost got it.
Ooh! That was a close call!
[BOTH gasp]
[BOY A] Hey! What's the
idea of botherin' us?!
Think you're a wise guy?
Come outta there!
We didn't start
trouble, you did!
Hey! Quiet, girlie!
You keep out of it!
[SPRITLE gasps]
This doesn't look good.
You better drive away
while you can.
Oh, yeah? Come on, boys,
let's smash his car up.
Wait a minute!
There's a whole buncha buttons
on his steering column.
This car must be the Mach 5.
You're right.
It does look like it!
And he's gotta be the
best racer in the world,
our hero, Speed Racer!
Could I have your
autograph, Speed?
Sign my book!
How 'bout autographin' my shirt?
Well, they changed their minds
pretty fast, didn't they?
[SPRITLE laughs]
My brother Speed's very popular.
[SPEED] A racer shouldn't
drive recklessly.
Making a corner, for instance.
You must slow down before it
and then speed up around it.
That means shifting down
at a certain point,
and then accelerating
for maximum traction.
It's gotta be done right.
Make just one mistake,
and it'll take a long time
until you're able to catch up.
And you can lose
control of your car,
which can be very dangerous.
[THUG A]
A regular wise guy.
You like showin' off for
those kids, don't cha, kid?
I was talking to my
friends here and not to you.
So keep out of it,
why don't you?
[THUG A]
Why should I?
I used to be a
professional racer myself.
But I don't have as
big a mouth as you, kid.
[BOY A]
Hey, you!
Get your hands off
my friend, Speed!
You keep out of this, squirt.
[BOYS groan]
[SPEED]
That wasn't nice.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
[SPEED] I was just giving them
some tips about driving.
Hey!
--[SPEED gasps]
--[THUG A groans]
[gasps]
[THUG C] Why don't you fight
instead of throwing things?
Get to work!
[THUG B]
Yeah! Um, good idea!
Hey, now, wait a minute.
There's no need for
any more trouble.
[THUG B yells]
--[SPEED grunting]
--[THUG B groaning]
--[THUG C groaning]
Had enough? Or would
you like some more?
[THUG C]
No! No more!
[THUG A]
Let's get outta here!
[THUG B]
Run for your life!
[ALL laugh]
[BOY B]
Hurray, Speed! Hurray!
You're a groovy fighter!
Tell us a racing story!
Is racing the only thing Speed
likes to talk about? Hm?!
[SPEED] Once I raced against
the trickiest team in the world.
They were called the
Car Acrobatic Team.
[BOY B]
Wow! Were they really acrobats?
[SPEED]
No, but their cars were.
[BOY C]
What could they do?
[SPRITLE]
And that's not all.
The Mach 5 can
even run underwater!
It can be a submarine
as well as an aeroplane?
--[TRIXIE] Spritle!
--[GIRL gasps]
Don't expect people to believe
the Mach 5 can do everything.
I didn't lie,
and she believes it!
Hi, my name is Janine.
This is a fabulous car.
I'm Trixie. I'm glad
you like the car.
Would you like
to go for a drive?
Do you mean it?
I sure would!
According to this speedometer,
this must be the
fastest car in the world!
You like the Mach 5, I guess.
Uh-huh. I wanna be a racer.
But I suppose I'll
never be able to be one
because my father hates cars.
I'm sorry to hear it.
[engine revs]
It goes fast,
just remember that.
[JANINE]
I will!
--[MAN gasps]
--[JANINE gasps]
[tires screech]
[MAN]
Down, Boy! Easy!
--Do something!
--[SPEED] Trixie!
[SPEED]
Whoa! Whoa, boy! Whoa!
[MAN groans]
[SPEED] Sir, are you all right?
Are you all right?!
[JANINE]
Oh, Papa!
Janine, were you
driving that car?
I was. I'm sorry, Papa.
[MAN] After I forbade
you to drive a car?!
I'll smash it into
a pile of junk!
[JANINE]
No, Papa! Don't touch it!
[groans]
[MAN grunting]
[JANINE]
No!
It doesn't belong to me!
I don't care. I'll smash it
because you were driving it.
No! You have no right
to smash it up like that!
Janine, get away!
--[SPEED] Hold it!
--[MAN] Huh?
I'm warning you. You'd better
not hit your daughter again.
[MAN]
I'm sorry.
I've been too upset
even to think.
He gets this way whenever
he thinks of cars!
All cars are weapons on wheels.
I hate them!
They should be destroyed,
every one of them.
When they're driven right,
they're perfectly safe, sir!
You don't understand!
Don't tell me about cars!
I lost my son in a car accident!
I have the best reason in
the world for hating cars.
[SPEED]
Sorry, I didn't know that, sir.
You remind me of my son--
the one that I lost.
Now I understand why
you acted the way you did.
I just couldn't help it.
Tell me about yourself.
Are you a student?
I used to be. Now I'm
a racing-- Oop!
[TRIXIE gasps]
[SPEED] I mean, now I'm working
at my father's factory.
[sighs]
[MAN]
Is that so?
Well, good luck, my boy.
Goodbye.
Janine! I want you to
come home. Right now!
Well...! Hmph.
[POPS] The paint was
scraped completely off.
But another car usually
causes more damage than this.
You've gotta be careful, Speed.
There are so many cars
on the roads today.
Okay, but I'm a good driver.
[SPARKY]
But a lot of drivers aren't.
And they're the ones
you have to look out for.
Listen to who's talking.
How old are you, Sparky?
[SPARKY]
Hm?
[ALL laugh]
[POPS gasps]
It's no laughing matter.
I read about accidents
in the paper every day!
More accidents. There are
some in the paper every day.
Ugh. We wouldn't have them
if we didn't have cars.
Janine, I don't want to catch
you around a car again.
I'll be right back, Papa.
[MAN]
Janine!
Where are you going?
Hm...
"New racing car
track opens today.
Well-known drivers
are to complete."
Hm...
[tires screech]
How's the track?
It's one of the best
I've ever driven on.
There's a terrific S-curve
and a hairpin turn.
Twenty more laps and you'll
be used to it, Speed.
[JANINE]
Oh, hello, Speed.
[SPEED]
Hi, Janine.
I read about the new track
and figured you'd be here.
Won't your father be angry
if he finds you came
out to the track?
I can't help it.
I've just got to drive fast.
[SPARKY] Go ahead, Speed.
Switch on the ignition.
[SPEED]
Okle-dokle!
It's fine now.
Huh?
What's comin' down the track?
[hooves clacking]
It's Papa!
[PEOPLE chattering]
--Janine! Easy. What did I say?!
--[horse neighs]
Didn't I forbid you to go near
any more cars? You did!
Now wait just a minute!
Don't interfere again!
I invited your daughter
to come out to the track.
It's my fault that she's here!
You're really a
professional racer!
Liar!
[gasps]
Leave him alone, Papa!
[MAN]
Get away!
They shouldn't build race
tracks for racing cars.
Here come the cars.
You'd better get out of the way.
[JANINE]
Papa!
[DRIVER A screams]
Hey!
[tires screech]
[DRIVER B screams]
Whoa!
[MAN] There... That gets
rid of some cars.
Papa... He should never
have gone out there. [sobs]
A catastrophe...
I'll make sure you pay
for what you've done!
It wasn't my fault the
horse got in their way!
[OFFICIAL A]
Come back here!
[THUG A grunts]
[OFFICIAL A groans]
We'll be glad to take care
of the rest of 'em, sir.
Just who are you men, anyway?
Just three friendly fellows
who don't like cars either.
I can use men like you.
Come to see me later.
[THUGS chuckling]
Looks like we found a sucker.
[tires screeching]
[cars honking]
Out of the way! I'm in a hurry!
This isn't a horse race track!
Listen, stop driving cars.
They're much too dangerous!
Out of my way, go on!
Can't you understand that
cars are rolling weapons?!
You're a nut and I'm
gonna give you a crack!
[groans]
[MAN]
Giddy-up!
[MAN] So there's only
one thing for us to do.
We must show people
how dangerous cars are.
[snickers]
That should be a cinch
for guys like us. Right?
[chuckles]
As long as we get
lots of loot for it.
[MAN] How about this
for a down payment?
[THUGS]
Look at that!
Gimme!
[THUGS grumbling]
You must never tell
anybody that I'm the one
behind this whole thing.
We won't, Mr. Trotter.
Word of honor.
--[THUGS snicker]
--[phone rings]
[THUGS gasp]
[JANINE]
Papa, it's Janine.
Janine! Where are you?
Where are you calling from?!
[JANINE]
Never mind.
Unless you change your mind
about cars, I won't come home!
Janine! Janine!
Operator! Operator!
What is it? Anything wrong
with the telephone?
--[TROTTER] Quiet!
--[THUGS yelp]
Just follow my orders
and get to work!
Or else!
[THUGS yelping]
Don't worry; we'll earn it!
What are we going to do?
[TRIXIE]
Do you have any ideas, Janine?
My father's so stubborn,
it's almost impossible to get
him to change his mind.
[sobs]
He was very upset.
Maybe if we leave him
alone for a while,
he'll calm down a bit.
And maybe it'd be better if you
stayed here for a while, Janine.
Oh, thank you. I will.
[THUG C]
You finished?
[THUG A]
Is that car all set to crash?
[THUG B] Yeah. Just wait'll
tomorrow, eh, boys?
[THUGS snicker]
[engine revs]
--[screams]
--[tires screech]
[PEOPLE screaming]
[cars honking]
That's just the beginning.
[THUGS laugh]
[THUGS laughing]
[POLICE A]
Halt! Stop! Stop!
Sorry, son, you can't
go into the city today.
We're having a tremendous
amount of accidents.
And because of the tremendous
amount of accidents,
metropolitan traffic has
been hopelessly snarled.
[JANINE]
What do you think's causing
all the accidents, Speed?
I haven't the vaguest idea!
[BARTENDER]
Well, I have a theory.
I figure the accidents
aren't accidental.
Somebody's causing them?
[TROTTER]
There!
Now, the next job's at
Pop Racer's motor factory.
[THUGS chuckling]
You want us to take care
of Speed Racer, eh?
But be careful that
the police don't get wise.
Heh, don't worry.
The cops'll never catch us.
[chuckles]
I just saw three strange men
running into the factory!
Robbers, I guess.
Let's go after them.
[SPARKY]
Okay.
I'm all ready!
My arms are aching for action.
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[THUG A grunts, groans]
I'll bet you're the guys
who've been causing
those terrible accidents!
So what if we are?
What are you gonna do about it?
C'mere, sonny.
[SPARKY]
Give yourselves up!
You're not gonna be able
to get away from us.
That's what you think.
Get 'em, boys.
[SPEED grunts]
[THUG A groans]
[THUG B groans]
--[SPEED grunting]
--[THUG A groaning]
--[THUG C groaning]
[THUB B grunts, groans]
Don't get them all so fast!
Save one of them for me!
[gasps]
[SPRITLE laughs]
[SPEED] Why did you fix
those cars so they'd crash?!
Answer me!
Mr. Trotter paid us to fix
those cars so they'd crash.
What?! You were paid
by Janine's father?!
[THUG C groans]
[TROTTER]
You!
What's the meaning of this?!
There's no use
lying, Mr. Trotter.
This man's already
confessed to the crime.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Get out of here! Go home!
Leave me alone!
If you were any
kind of decent man,
you'd go to the
police and tell them.
Get out, I said!
But before you do,
tell me where my daughter is.
Where is she hiding?
Janine is with
Trixie in a new car,
and they're driving toward
the Craggy Peak Mountains.
Mr. Trotter, I fixed
the brakes on that car.
Just as you ordered me to, sir.
My daughter's in danger.
[SPEED groans]
[TROTTER]
Giddy-up!
Better hurry, Speed!
[gasps]
The brakes aren't working!
[JANINE gasps]
Now it's impossible to stop.
Try the emergency brake!
We're going even faster now!
[TROTTER]
Whoa!
Come on. Hop in my car.
It's the only way you'll
catch up to your daughter.
[TROTTER grunts]
You'll never catch
her like that.
Come on!
[screams]
I swore never to ride in a car.
Giddy-up!
Okay!
--[BOTH scream]
--[tires screech]
[gasps]
[TRIXIE gasps, grunts]
[tires screeching]
[TRIXIE] Something's wrong
with the steering!
[BOTH scream]
[gasps]
[tires screech]
[SPEED]
Trixie!
Speed, help Janine!
[SPEED]
Hm?
[gasps]
Janine! Janine!
[TROTTER]
Wait!
Give her to me.
I'll take my daughter
to a hospital.
[horse neighs]
[TROTTER]
Whoa! Easy, boy, easy!
Whoa! Come on,
take it easy! Hey!
What's the matter with you?
Come on, let's go!
Listen, Mr. Trotter.
Your daughter needs
medical help right away.
And that horse'll never get
her to the hospital in time!
[TRIXIE] We don't care
how you feel about cars.
Janine is more important!
[SPEED grunts]
[TRIXIE]
Hurry, Speed!
[JANINE] Oh, thank you.
Thank you all for everything!
[POPS]
Chim Chim!
--[JANINE giggles]
--[door clicks]
[gasps]
--Papa!
--My daughter!
[JANINE] Oh, Papa! Why didn't
you come to visit me sooner?
I've been in jail, paying for
the crimes I've committed.
It wasn't until today
that they released me.
Promise you'll never do
anything like that again.
[TROTTER]
I promise, Janine.
I've learned my lesson.
Oh, let's forget it.
It's time you were
both going home.
I have a present
for you, Mr. Trotter--
a sports car I built
with my own hands.
It'll never get tired, and it
runs even better than a horse.
[TROTTER]
Thanks, Mr. Racer.
I realize now that a car
can be either a weapon
or a lifesaver. It all
depends on who's driving it.
[whistle blows]
Shall I carry you across
the street, old lady?
Hang on.
Thanks, young man.
[THUG A chuckles]
Okay, whoever's next,
just hop on my back.
[dog barks]
[TROTTER] I gave them
orders that, from now on,
they'd better help
whomever they can.
Very good idea.
Janine, I'm going to let
you be a racing driver.
Thanks, Papa.
That's great!
Speed'll give you
racing driver lessons.
And you'd better pay
very close attention.
I shall.
[whistle blows]
[THUG A yelps, groans]
[ALL laugh]
[NARRATOR] More thrills
and excitement lie ahead
in the next thrilling
episode of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪