♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR] Deep in the southern
part of South America,
Speed is preparing to
compete in the famous
Southern Hemisphere
Pineapple Grand Prix.
According to this map,
part of the course runs through
some of the most dangerous
and unexplored territory
in the southern hemisphere.
And it runs through this valley
called the Valley
of Destruction.
I'm not sure I like that
name. It's frightening!
So's the racing course,
I bet. It'll be tough!
I'm afraid you're right.
Not many will finish.
At least, that's what I heard.
Mm, and no wonder! Look at
all those twists and turns!
Speed'll be one of the few
to cross the finish line.
But only if I'm lucky, Sparky.
You'll have more than luck
riding with you, Speed.
You're quick and
skillful and experienced
and very, very strong.
--[SPEED] Hmm? Hmm...
--[TRIXIE laughs]
[knocking]
[TRIXIE]
Coming!
Oh, hello.
Excuse me, I'm looking
for Mr. Speed Racer.
[TRIXIE]
He's right here.
Hello, I'm Speed Racer.
My name's Eloisa Hazard,
the sister of Hap,
one of the drivers you'll
be competing against.
More than anything in the world,
I want to see my brother
win the Grand Prix.
Won't you let him win?
You're asking me to
lose the Grand Prix?
Well, my brother wants you
to lose, and so do I, Speed.
But that would be cheating,
and I've never done anything
illegal in my life, ever!
But it would mean so much to
my brother and me. Please.
I'll have to ask
you to leave here!
Oh!
The poor girl fainted!
I'll call a doctor!
[TRIXIE]
Hurry!
Speed, why are you so angry?
You know I'm angry because of
what that girl asked me to do!
Well, maybe she didn't realize
that what she asked you
was so wrong!
[NARRATOR] A section of
the city of Theodado,
where Eloisa Hazard lives
with her brother, Hap.
[tires screech]
[HAP]
Hey!
This is my sister!
What happened to her?!
She came to see me and then
she fainted. That's all.
She fainted? Or maybe you
and your friends beat her up
so I'll have to take care
of her and won't have time
--to be in the race!
--What an idea!
Get out of here!
Eloisa, speak to me.
Tell me you'll be all right.
[TRIXIE]
Speed!
[SPEED]
Huh?
[TRIXIE] Let them go,
Speed. Don't be angry.
I wonder why Hap spoke
to you the way he did.
[SPEED]
Huh?
Get out of the way,
you're blocking the road!
Get out of your car!
We're looking for something.
What is it? What're
you looking for, sir?
[THUG B]
Quiet!
Come over here!
--[THUG B] Let's get him!
--[THUG C] Yeah!
[yells]
[yelps]
[shrieks]
[THUG A yells]
[TRIXIE] You say that
money isn't the only reason
your brother wants
to win the race?
That's right. If he wins, he has
a chance of becoming the manager
of a big factory
that builds cars.
But he's been acting
very strangely lately.
Winning that race is all that
matters to my poor brother.
I wish I could help him...
And you need money so
the doctors can make you
completely well.
Right... They said that making
me well would be very expensive.
Exactly where is the car factory
that may hire your brother?
I don't know. He never told me.
[TRIXIE]
Hmm...
--[grunting]
--[THUG D chuckling]
Well, I won't be
patient any longer.
You'd better tell me what you
did with the King's Jewel.
Okay, give him a
little more persuasion.
[THUG A]
Sure!
[BOSS] I know you
stole that King's Jewel
and it's worth a million bucks!
And you used the Southern
Hemisphere Grand Prix
as an excuse to smuggle
it into this country!
Well, you'd better tell me
where it is right now!
Tell me which car that
jewel is hidden in.
Talk. Talk!
It's not in any of the cars.
Tell me where you
hid that jewel!
In one of the pineapples.
You put the jewel in
one of the pineapples
to be used in the race!
No wonder we couldn't find it!
I don't know which
pineapple it's in.
Don't worry about
that, I'll find it!
[laughs]
I'll find it no matter what!
[ANNOUNCER] The Southern
Hemisphere Pineapple Grand Prix
is about to start!
And because the pineapple is the
national fruit of our country,
each driver will carry
a pineapple with him
during the race.
At the starting signal, the
drivers must run to that pile
of pineapples, and
grab one of the fruits
before he can leap
into his car.
He must then carry the pineapple
with him during the entire race.
The drivers are ready. The
signal is about to be given.
Stand by!
[ANNOUNCER]
There they go!
[THUG B] We're over one of
the pineapples now, Mr. Porson.
[PORSON]
Good!
We'll find out if that's the one
the King's Jewel is hidden in.
Bring it up here.
[THUG B]
Yes, sir.
Huh?!
It's empty!
[THUG B]
Empty!
Empty...
Empty.
Empty! Empty!
Which one is that jewel in?!
We may have to
look for that jewel
in every pineapple down there!
I know that! Keep looking!
That oil will make
the track slippery!
[MAN yelling]
They're empty!
It's not in them!
[PORSON] It's in one of
the pineapples in the race,
but which one?!
That jewel's gotta be
in one of the pineapples
we haven't opened yet!
I figured that out!
Now, come on, we'll
check the rest of them.
Now I'm entering
the Unknown Forest.
Bah! Nothing! Huh...?
This must be the Unknown Forest.
[gasps]
I've gotta jump over this
log and get out of here.
[gasps]
[THUG E]
Stay right where you are!
[guitar strumming]
[THUG F] We've been waiting
for you, Speed Racer.
[SPEED]
Huh?
[THUG F] We've been waiting
patiently for you to come along
so that we could get
that precious pineapple
out of your car.
Oh yeah? I think
you're friends of Hap's
and you just don't want
me to finish the race!
Just give us the pineapple
and keep your mouth shut!
[THUG E] Why waste time
asking him for it, mi amigos?
He won't give it to us?
So, go ahead and take it!
[THUGS yelping]
If I don't keep this pineapple
with me at all times,
I'll be disqualified
from the race.
So I'm sorry, gentleman,
but you can't have it!
Get him!
[gasps]
[yells]
[sighs]
That'll take care of them.
But Hap. Why's he trying to
win the race from me this way?
Why doesn't he try to
win it fair and square?
Stop, Speed!
What's the matter?
What do you want?
My pineapple! One of
your men took it from me!
[SPEED]
What're you talking about?!
It was your men who stopped
me back in the forest
and tried to take my
pineapple away from me!
What're you talking about?!
Why don't you try to win
this race fair and square?!
I'm trying to do that, Speed.
But how can I when your
men took my pineapple?!
That must be how you
win so many races.
By using unfair
tricks! By cheating!
[SPEED] Those are
fighting words! Come on!
[HAP]
Okay, then let's fight!
[SPEED]
I'm ready! Come on!
[SPEED coughs]
[HAP]
See you when the race is over!
[SPEED]
I can't let him win...
Calling the Mach 5.
Come in, Speed.
Trixie calling the Mach 5!
I'm in the middle of a race,
Trixie! Don't talk to me now!
Can't you wait till it's over?
Speed, listen to me! Eloisa's
brother Hap has got to win!
Please let him!
Why should I let him win?!
I'm out to win myself! Now
sign off, and don't bother me!
But Hap must win so that
he can pay for the doctors
to make his sister well.
And besides, Hap
would then be hired
to manage a big car factory.
That would solve all
their money problems.
Please let him win, Speed!
It doesn't matter to me what his
reasons are for wanting to win!
I wouldn't be playing fair if I
let him win the race on purpose!
[TRIXIE]
But, Speed!
[SPEED] I'll see you when
the race is over, Trixie!
But Eloisa's ill!
They must have some money!
Please let him win, Speed!
Speed? Speed! Speed!
Ahh... There seems to be
no end to this swamp land.
I've got to go faster.
I'm losing too much time!
--[rumbling]
--[gasps]
[SPEED] A landslide!
It's liable to trap me!
[engine sputtering]
[gasps]
Hang on, Hap! I'll try to pull
you out! I'll be right there!
[HAP]
Hurry!
[engine revving]
[SPEED]
Okay, Hap, you're safe now!
[HAP]
Huh?
[gasps]
I got you out. You can
go on with the race.
Where are we?
The Valley of Destruction.
[HAP]
Destruction? No wonder...
If I hadn't come along,
you'd've been trapped here.
It's as simple as that.
I owe you my life, Speed.
I won't forget...
But I'm still gonna try to beat
you in the race, and I will!
And what's more, I'm not going
to give this pineapple back!
It's mine!
You're wrong, Hap. It belongs to
me! You took it out of my car!
I say it's mine!
No, Hap!
What's that plane up to?!
[THUG A]
Hold it right there!
Grab that pineapple, men!
[ALL yell]
Chim Chim!
[THUG D] Hmm?!
Get the pineapple from him!
[THUG A]
Come on, monkey. Hand it over!
Quick, throw it, Chim Chim!
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[SPARKY]
Got it!
Huh? Trixie!
[gasps]
[TRIXIE]
Run, Chim Chim! Run!
Come back here with that
pineapple! Give it to me!
Come back here! Come back!
Now hand it over! Ah!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
That was a rock you caught!
[SPRITLE] Okay, Chim Chim,
throw a forward pass!
[THUG A]
Got it!
After them!
[TRIXIE]
Run, Spritle! Run!
[SPEED]
Got it!
[TRIXIE]
Go, Speed, go!
Speed got away
with the pineapple!
We did our best, Boss,
but we were outsmarted.
[PORSON]
Boneheads!
We'll have to get the
pineapple at the finish line.
I'm comin' down
to getcha. Hang on!
Wonder where they're going
and what they're up to now.
Let's go and meet Speed
at the finish line.
We'll just have
time to get there.
[HAP]
Stop! Stop! Stop your car!
Give me back that
pineapple! Pull over!
Pull over! I want
that pineapple!
[ANNOUNCER]
The cars have now been driven
almost 25 hundred miles,
and in a few moments,
the winner will be
crossing the finish line.
I'm able to see them!
Hap Hazard is now out in front,
but Speed Racer is
driving a close second!
Now Speed's ahead, now he's not!
They're fighting it out!
They have one more mile to go!
Ladies and gentleman,
right now, it's a dead heat!
Give me back that
pineapple, Speed!
[ANNOUNCER] Only half a
mile more! Here they come!
[ANNOUNCER]
Speed wins!
[CROWD cheering]
Now, ladies and gentleman,
we must check to
see that the winner
still has in his
possession the pineapple
with which he began the Southern
Hemisphere Pineapple Grand Prix.
Speed, will you please
show us your pineapple?
[SPEED gasps]
[SPEED]
It's gone!
Thanks, Chim Chim!
I hate to do this to Speed,
but it's the only way.
Take the pineapple
over to Hap's car
and put it in without
anybody noticing.
[SPEED]
I can't understand it.
I don't know where that
pineapple could've gone.
[ANNOUNCER]
If you don't have the pineapple,
you're disqualified.
Mr. Hazard, do you have
a pineapple in your car?
[gasps]
I've got the pineapple right
here! I'm the winner of
the Southern Hemisphere
Pineapple Grand Prix!
I'm the winner!
Look, I won!
[gasps]
[PORSON]
Huh?!
Where's the jewel?! Where?!
What happened to it?!
It was supposed to be
in one of the pineapples!
He lied to me about it!
Speed Racer was disqualified
because he didn't have
a pineapple in his car,
so the winner of the
Grand Prix is Hap Hazard!
[CROWD cheering]
As winner, Mr. Hazard will
be awarded the top prize
of $10,000, and a ten-year
supply of pineapples!
However, Mr. Hazard has
generously said that he wants
to give the ten-year supply
of pineapples to you, his fans!
The King's Jewel must be
in one of those pineapples!
Let's get it!
[THUG D]
Yeah!
[PORSON]
Outta the way, brats!
Not in this one so far!
Err... Let me see now...
I never saw a man
like pineapples
the way those men seem to...
[SPRITLE]
I'm hungry!
Yum! Yummy! Yum!
Huh?! Ah!
[OFFICER] A diamond!
This is a mammoth diamond!
[PORSON]
I know! Isn't it beautiful?!
This is the King's Jewel!
It's the King's Jewel, all
right! I'll return it to him!
[THUG A, THUG D]
You and your smart ideas!
Now you'll get that job!
And, from now on,
there'll be enough money for the
doctors to make you well again!
[BOTH laughing]
[HAP] I told you I had
to win, Eloisa, and I did!
And now everybody knows
I am a better racer than Speed!
And our troubles are over!
We'll never have to worry
about anything again!
[BOTH laughing]
[SPEED]
Oh, Trixie.
You can blame me for
Hap being the winner
of the Grand Prix, Speed.
I told Chim Chim to
give him the pineapple.
I know why you did, Trixie,
and it's for the best after all.
[TRIXIE, SPEED laugh]
Thank you very much.
[chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
Be sure to see the next
exciting episode
of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪