♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[SPEED] This mysterious car
contains the most powerful
and dangerous racing car
engine in the world.
[engine revs]
[SPEED] Pops warned us to
keep away from that car.
That it could be dangerous.
But I had to see for myself
what kind of engine
was beneath that hood.
And so, I sneaked into the house
where the car was being stored
and discovered that
the engine was the GRX.
The famous GRX! It was hard
to believe, yet there it was.
I had to find out
what it was like
to start up the fastest
car in the world.
Sounds fabulous.
Powerful.
I've gotta drive it.
It's almost as fast
as the speed of sound!
It's really power-packed!
[gasps]
[SPEED] I was traveling so fast
that the road became a blur.
I felt as if, somehow,
I was traveling
into another dimension.
A dimension reached
only through speed.
And then, I lost consciousness.
[sighs]
[SPEED] With Spritle
and Chim Chim's help,
Pops had escaped from
the strange people
who owned the car I was driving.
Now Pops was trying to
save me from crashing.
There he is!
[POPS]
He's unconscious!
[SPRITLE]
What do we do?
[POPS]
We've gotta stop that car!
[CHIM CHIM yelps, gibbers]
[SPEED groans]
Quick, Chim Chim; try to
put your foot on the break!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[gasps]
Put your foot on
the break, Chim Chim!
Don't be a wise guy!
[babbles]
C'mon, Chim Chim, use
your feet. Like this!
No!
You're not using your head!
[POPS]
No! That's not what I mean!
[BOTH gasp]
[CHIM CHIM gibbering]
[brakes squeal]
[BOTH gasp, sigh]
[SPRITLE]
Nice going, Chim Chim!
[CHIM CHIM babbles]
[POPS, SPRITLE]
Speed!
Speed! Hey!
[car rumbles]
[POPS]
Hm?
[GOON 1] We want our car
back! Get outta the way!
[grunting]
Hurray! Hurray!
[BOTH gasp]
[GOON 1 groans]
[grunting]
[cheering]
[grunting continues]
[GOON 3]
Oh! Oh! No! No!
[SPRITLE, CHIM CHIM grunt]
[grunting]
[BOTH gasp]
[SPRITLE] Sissy! You're
scared of Pops! Sissies!
[growls]
[SPEED pants]
[MOM]
My son...
Wake up, Speed.
There's something bothering him.
Something to do with that car.
[gasps]
He'll be all right after
I give him the treatment.
Speed's suffering
from the high speed
at which he traveled.
It's affected his coordination
and there's only one way
to bring him out of it.
It'll be worse for
me than for him.
Do you have to go
through with it, Pops?
Yes, I do.
I'm sorry to have to
do this to you, son.
But it's the only way.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[POPS]
C'mon. Snap out of it, Speed!
[TRIXIE]
Stop it, Pops! That's enough!
He's all right now,
can't you see?
[grunts]
[groans]
[SPEED laughs]
It's no laughing matter.
We've been very worried
about you, Speed!
Five racers crashed trying
to test that engine.
One of them was Ben Cranem,
the man who designed it.
There isn't a man on Earth who
can handle the GRX's power.
It's a speed monster. And
even though you travel fast,
you can't win a race with it.
The speed and power in
the GRX has a peculiar,
uncontrollable effect on
the driver's coordination.
Son, you've got to
keep away from that car.
Otherwise, you'll
meet the same fate
as those other unfortunate men.
We don't wanna
lose you, Speed.
[ANNOUNCER] We are about
to begin the final trials
for the Oriental Grand Prix.
The trials today and tomorrow
will determine the starting
positions for the big race!
The first two cars in the
trials will be the GRX,
driven by Loomis Towcar, and the
Mach 5, driven by Speed Racer.
It's only the trial today.
Don't try to beat the car.
Hold back a little.
[ANNOUNCER] The first trial will
begin in exactly one minute.
Stand by!
Hey, Loomis. You'll need the
special formula so's you can
stand the terrific
speed of the GRX.
[coughs]
If you get thirsty, remember
you'll get water when it's over.
So just be patient.
[growls] I'm thirsty already!
I feel as if I could drink
a gallon of water right now!
That's too bad. But
you'll just have to wait,
because the formula won't
work if you drink any water.
And if that formula wore off
while you're driving GRX,
you'd get so scared you'd
lose control of the car
and smash to smithereens!
So forget about drinking
water for a while... Or else!
[ANNOUNCER]
Thirty seconds before the start!
The Mach 5 and the GRX
are now in position
at the starting line.
Stand by!
I hope he doesn't try
to outrace that car!
[ANNOUNCER]
Four seconds!
Three, two, one! Start!
[laughs]
He's traveling fast now,
but his speed's even picking up.
Don't try to beat 'im!
Keep your own pace!
[SPEED]
I know the Mach 5 doesn't have
enough power to win,
but I don't like to
get beaten like this.
I've got to have water!
[groans]
[ANNOUNCER]
The GRX has picked up speed
and is now leading
by five seconds!
I'm falling further behind!
[LOOMIS] Water! I've gotta
have a drink of water!
[GOON 1]
Huh?! Is he trying to crash?!
[LOOMIS]
Ah! I don't feel so good.
[gasps]
[LOOMIS]
Ah! I can't stand it any longer!
[tires squeal]
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[screams]
[screaming continues]
[sirens wail]
[gasps]
The driver of the
GRX was very lucky.
Apparently, he
wasn't injured but,
it seems as though he fainted.
The doctors will check
him at the hospital.
[ORIANA]
Speed.
Speed. How would you
like to drive the GRX?
I assure you, if you
were driving it,
you'd win the
Oriental Grand Prix.
Me drive the monster?
[ORIANA laughs]
I'm sure you'd be able to handle
a car with all that power.
I'll get it repaired right now!
I want to drive the GRX.
I want to feel all
that power again.
Well, you're going to have
the opportunity, Speed.
Gentlemen, I think
our problem is solved.
Speed Racer's going to win
the Oriental Grand Prix,
only, he's going
to win it for us.
[TRIXIE] That's funny. I don't
see Speed down there anywhere.
[POPS]
Hm...
He left the Mach 5
down there on the course.
He's acting very strangely.
I wonder where he went.
I don't see Chim Chim either!
Pops. Why don't you make
an official complaint
to the police department?
After all, they dug up the GRX
from a graveyard, didn't they?
[POPS] Yes. But if I brought
the case to the police,
it would get a lot of publicity.
And other people would
learn about the GRX
and try to build
an engine like it,
with just as much power
and just as dangerous!
You're right. And other
drivers would crack up.
[GOON 1] It's finished!
The GRX is repaired!
[gasps]
[ORIANA]
That was quick!
[SPEED]
What a fabulous car!
The GRX!
You're not afraid to
drive it, Speed, are you?
I'm anxious.
[BOTH chuckle]
[coughs]
[engine revs]
I can't imagine
where Speed can be!
--[radio beeps]
--[TRIXIE gasps]
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
Chim Chim!
[gibbering continues]
Chim Chim's trying his best
to tell us where Speed is
and what he's doing!
C'mon! Maybe we can
find them both!
He's a terrific driver!
[gasps]
[POPS] You're still under
some strange spell!
I've got to snap you out of it!
[grunting]
Pops, are you sure
you're not hurting him?
[POPS]
I'm doing it for his own good!
[gasps]
[POPS]
Now, let's go home.
[POPS, SPEED grunt]
I wanna drive the GRX!
I wanna drive that car!
[GOON 1 growls]
I've gotta catch him!
What happened to the key?!
[CURLY]
The GRX. I'm gonna drive it.
I'm the only driver who has a
right to sit behind that wheel.
[CHIM CHIM babbles]
[SPRITLE gasps] I'll bet
that's a key for the GRX!
[SPARKY] Mm-Mm...
Chim Chim did a good job!
I hope Speed'll be okay now.
Oh, poor Speed.
He'd better snap outta that!
Water! I've gotta have water!
[gasps]
--[sighs]
--Speed! What's the matter?
What's wrong?
I-I'm scared. Please,
Pops. Slow down!
I can't stand moving fast!
[SPEED whimpers]
[POPS]
But I'm only going 60!
But even that seems very
fast to me right now!
Pops, please slow down!
Spritle, please switch
off the light.
[SPRITLE]
Mm-hm.
[SPEED gasps, whimpers]
No! Stop it! Stop the projector!
Keep your eyes open
and watch the film.
[SPEED]
No, Pops, I can't stand anymore!
[SPEED gasps]
I'm trying to cure you, son.
Watch the picture.
[SPEED]
No. I can't. I can't!
A professional racing driver
is not afraid of driving fast.
[SPEED panting]
[phone rings]
Yes, that's right.
This is Pops Racer.
What? It was! You're sure?
And you analyzed the
chemicals? I see...
Thanks very much.
Who was that on the phone?
Dr. Skuller's his name.
The cerebral physiologist?
Yes. On our way here, we stopped
for him to examine Speed
and he just reported.
He suspects that Speed
inhaled some V Gas.
V Gas? What's that? Hm?
It sharpened his
reflective nerves
so that he could respond faster
and it removed every
fear of velocity.
But now he seems
just the opposite.
He's afraid of going fast.
When the V Gas wears off,
or if the victim drinks water,
he reacts differently
and becomes terrified of
even the slowest speeds.
Son, you've gotta overcome
this fear of speed
before the Oriental
Grand Prix starts.
Now, Speed, I'm going to give
you another treatment.
[engines purr]
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen.
In exactly 30 minutes,
The Grand Prix of the
Orient will start.
Right now, all cars are getting
their final tune-ups.
Here you are, Speed.
The Mach 5 has a good
chance to win, Speed,
as long as you're not
afraid to go all out
and drive it the way
I built it to be driven.
But I'm scared. I can't help it.
Be a man and don't let anybody
know how afraid you are.
It takes more courage to do
that, Speed, than anything else!
You mustn't disappoint us, son.
You'll come in second, Speed,
because I'm gonna be the
winner of the Grand Prix!
Let me give you
some advice, Curly.
You better get out
of the race now,
because you're not going to win!
And I'll tell you
something else.
No human being on Earth
can last 30 laps in this car.
Now I'll tell you
something, Mr. Racer.
Speed doesn't have
a chance to win
because he's scared
to travel fast.
He's wrong.
[ANNOUNCER]
The Oriental Grand Prix
will start in
exactly 90 seconds!
All drivers are now in
their starting positions,
awaiting the signal
for ignition.
[SPEED]
What am I gonna do? I'm scared!
[ANNOUNCER]
Start engines!
[engines purr]
[engines roar]
[ANNOUNCER] The Mach 5 is caught
in the center of the pack
and, at this point, does not
look to be a possible winner.
It's reported that Speed is
not in top physical condition.
[ANNOUNCER]
At the end of the first lap,
The fantastic GRX is
leading by five seconds,
and already looks to be
the possible winner.
Go, go, go, go!
[POPS] Don't let anybody
know how afraid you are!
The Mach 5 can win if you're
not afraid to drive it
the way I build it to be driven!
[CURLY]
No one back there.
I'm going so fast; nobody'll
be able to catch up to me.
[POPS] Don't be scared. The
frightened guy finishes last.
Go, Speed, go!
If you're scared,
just step on the gas.
Push that accelerator
down to the floor!
[POPS] I built the
Mach 5 to win, Speed,
and with it, you can win!
[ANNOUNCER]
In the 15th lap,
the GRX is now leading
by fully half a minute.
This amazing car is now expected
to break all existing records.
The Mach 5 is in second place.
C'mon, Speed! You can win!
[POPS] Speed, if you're still
afraid, get out of the race.
If you're not scared,
then do what you want!
And I'll bet what
you want is to win!
[POPS laughs]
I'm okay and I'm gonna
do my best to win.
[CURLY growls]
Water. I've got to have water!
[ANNOUNCER]
The 27th lap.
And the GRX goes into the pit.
[GOON 1]
Uh-oh.
Get back in that car!
[gasps]
[grunts]
He lost too much time!
I'm afraid he's not going
to be able to catch up!
[engine sputters]
You'll never be able to
catch up to me, Speed.
[whimpers]
[yells]
[CURLY]
It's too fast!
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER]
The GRX is out of the race
and the Mach 5 pulls
into the lead!
I didn't know that Curly
was the son of the man
who invented the GRX!
Neither did I, Speed.
I would've stopped him if
I'd known who he really was.
Isn't it strange?
Both father and son were
destroyed by that engine.
It proves something:
That traveling fast is
important to win a race,
but it's not the
most important thing.
Right!
It takes the combination
of a good driver,
and a really fine car in
tip-top shape to win a race.
[BOTH laugh]
Let's go home.
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪