♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[SPEED]
Two days before the start
of the Trans-Africa Grand Prix,
I had finished
checking the course
and was flying back
to Nairobi in a small plane.
On board, I met
Professor Carnivory,
who was on his way to
check into a story about
monsters living near
a mysterious mountain.
But the pilot took
the professor prisoner,
and they all bailed out!
I crash-landed in the jungle
near a huge monster gorilla!
[SPEED] I saw a strange tank
make its way through the jungle.
It headed for a mysterious
island out on the center
of a lake.
As the tank reached the lake,
a bridge came out of the water.
And before the bridge could be
lowered into the water again,
I started across!
But I found myself
in a land of gorillas.
[gorillas roaring]
[roars]
[SPEED gasps]
[yells]
[SPEED groans]
[gorillas roaring]
[panting]
[yelps]
[grunts]
[SPEED gasps]
[SPEED groans]
[SPEED screams]
[SMASHER snickers]
That's the end of
that nosey young man.
Whoever tries to sneak onto this
island meets a similar fate.
And don't forget,
Professor Carnivory,
that although
you're my guest here,
the same thing will happen
to you if you cross me.
We developed those
monster gorillas,
now I want to try
my process on humans!
I want to build
an army of giant men!
[CARNIVORY]
I refuse to help you!
[SMASHER]
Is that so?
Well, I think I can
persuade you to
change your mind and cooperate!
Professor, I want you
to meet someone.
Meet someone?
[SMASHER]
Mm-hmm!
[footsteps]
Please come in, Professor.
I hope you both have
a productive talk.
[CARNIVORY]
Wait! Where are you going?!
[MAN laughing]
[CARNIVORY]
Wha--?
[laughing continues]
[MAN] It's been a long time,
Professor Carnivory.
[CARNIVORY]
Professor Loon!
[LOON] You recognize me, then.
After 20 long years.
Excellent.
Come, let us drink to the past
when we used to work
together so long ago.
And to the future
because, from now on,
we'll be working together again,
Professor Carnivory.
Wait a minute.
I never agreed to work
for General Smasher.
[LOON]
Eh?!
Don't worry.
You'll agree to work for him.
If you refuse,
you'll be finished forever.
[CARNIVORY]
But it's impossible to turn
small animals and insects
into huge monsters.
[LOON] Is it? You're about
to change your mind. Watch!
[CARNIVORY]
That's incredible!
I've never seen
such a huge spider!
Of course, you haven't.
But this used to be
a small spider
no bigger than the end
of your thumb, Professor.
If you agree to work with me
in developing
a human army of giants,
it will be the opportunity
of your lifetime!
How about it,
Professor Carnivory?
Will you agree
to work me with me
in the development of
an army of giant men?
[laughs]
So, you won't work with me, eh?
[CARNIVORY] I'll respect your
passion for the scientific study
of making these
creatures so large,
but I cannot go along with
General Smasher's plan
to build an army of giants.
[LOON]
But it's for patriotic reasons.
We want to rescue
our country from oppression,
and we need an army to do it!
[CARNIVORY gasps]
[LOON laughs]
I have quite a difficult time
with this little fellow.
He often escapes by biting
through his chains.
Only today, we've managed to
recapture him and lock him up.
We put extra chains on him
and gave him something
to make him sleepy.
But I'm afraid it's wearing off
and he'll wake up now.
[gorilla growls, roars]
Now he should begin
to get violent.
[CARNIVORY] And you want me
to help make human beings
like that; an army of
men like that?! Never!
I don't care what you do to me,
I will not help you
build monsters.
Come on, don't be a fool.
Think of the
scientific values of
creating a supersized
army of men.
[SPEAKER]
Professor Loon, Professor Loon.
Please come to the
monitor room immediately.
A strange vehicle
is approaching the island.
It looks as if
this underwater bridge
leads to that island up ahead.
I wonder what could be
on that strange island.
[SPRITLE] I hope Chim Chim's
all right. And Speed, too!
[SPRITLE]
Oh, look!
[SPRITLE gasps]
That looks to me as if
it's some kind of a door.
[BOTH gasp]
--[SPRITLE gasping]
--[TRIXIE grunting]
[TRIXIE]
Oh! A strange place!
[SPRITLE] I sure don't
like the looks of it.
[SMASHER]
Very interesting.
An amphibious car with
a girl and a child in it.
Dr. Loon, get rid
of them permanently!
Wait, dear General Smasher,
let me capture them.
I have a great plan.
There's something
spooky around here.
[SPRITLE]
There's the end of the tunnel!
[BOTH]
Tanks up ahead!
[BOTH scream]
[LOON laughs]
[LOON] At last, the final plans
can be carried out.
He can't refuse now;
he wouldn't dare.
[chuckles]
[LOON] Professor, I have
something quite interesting
to show you.
I don't care.
I'm not interested.
[LOON]
Aren't you? We'll see...
Come and see.
I've captured some prisoners.
It shouldn't be hard
for you to imagine
what I plan to do with them.
[door clicks]
Ah! Come in, Professor. Come in!
Go ahead.
You'll be interested in
what we're going to do.
All right, lower the prisoners.
[gasps]
Hey, what's the big idea?!
Take me down off this rope!
Do as he says.
Let them off those ropes.
They're innocent children;
they haven't done
anything to anyone!
I'll let them go
if you change your mind
and agree to work for me.
How about it?
[CARNIVORY]
Huh?!
[lion growling]
[BOTH scream]
Stop it!
I demand you get those
children out of there!
I already told you.
I'm willing to let them go...
under one condition.
[SPRITLE]
Please, please, let us go!
[lion roars]
[TRIXIE, SPRITLE gasp]
Trixie, I'm scared.
That's just the
beginning, Professor.
There's no escaping in there.
[water splashing]
[lion roars]
--[TRIXIE, SPRITLE gasp]
--[LOON laughs]
The water is filled with that
infamous fish from the Amazon
called the piranha.
They can strip an elephant
to bones in a minute.
Agree to work with me in
developing an army of giants
or I'll lower those
children into the water.
Save them, Professor. Say that
you agree to work with me.
You're not being fair, Doctor.
I have nothing to do
with those children,
so why should their
lives depend on me?
Now please get them out of
there before it's too late!
[TRIXIE, SPRITLE gasping]
Just a few feet more
and they'll be in.
[TRIXIE, SPRITLE gasping]
[LOON giggles]
All right, Professor.
You're responsible
for what happens next.
They're going to lower the rope.
All right, lower away!
Lower them into the water!
[CARNIVORY]
Wait!
[roaring]
[SPEED gasps]
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
You're here!
Oh, Chim Chim! I didn't expect
to find you on the island!
But I'm glad to see a friend!
[BOTH laughing]
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[SPEED]
What? Where?
Oh, the Mach 5!
That's it, all right.
Oh, I'm glad to see the Mach 5.
I was afraid I wouldn't
see my old friends again.
There still may be hope.
[gasps]
Trixie and Spritle!
Chim Chim, what happened to
Trixie and Spritle?
Do you know where
they are right now?
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
That means you don't have
any idea where they are.
Well, this is such a big island,
so I might be able to find them!
Come on, hurry!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[CARNIVORY]
The country of Giltar.
That's what it was
called 20 years ago.
Many people have forgotten it
or want to forget it.
Giltar was a country
that loved war.
What kind of men
are holding us prisoner?
[CARNIVORY] The men from Giltar
who lived only for war.
And they're planning
to start another war.
By the way, I met a young man
who might be the one
you're looking for.
We were on a plane together.
His name was Speed.
[TRIXIE gasps]
I feel very sorry for him.
He just happened to be on that
plane when the trouble began.
It was just a coincidence.
Professor! Do you know
what happened to Speed?
Well, I imagine
the plane crashed.
--[SPEED grunts]
--[tires screech]
[gasps]
[gorillas roaring]
This must be where they feed
and keep those mammoth gorillas!
[gasps] Tanks!
Let's get out of here!
[engine revs]
[SPEED]
Hang on!
[PILOT A]
Hmm...
This is a small island;
he can't get very far.
Come on, men,
let's look for him!
I've seen that young man
somewhere before.
I'll bet he's Speed Racer
who was on the plane
with that professor.
[SPEED yells]
[BOTH grunt]
What's up out there?
What's goin' on, eh?
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[PILOT B groans]
[SPEED grunts]
They can both nap.
That way, we'll have no more
trouble from either of them.
[LOON]
Here they are, Professor.
The amazing machines which
make everything supersized.
[CARNIVORY]
Hmm...
[LOON] We'll see how well
they work on humans when we
--use those children!
--[gasps]
[LOON]
What's the matter?
You wouldn't be so cruel,
would you, Doctor?
You wouldn't turn those two
children into mammoth monsters!
In scientific experiments,
one must have no personal
feelings, Professor.
We must proceed only for
the sake of pure science.
And... the only way
we can be sure
if our process can
make giants out of humans
is to try it out
on these prisoners.
[LOON laughs]
You must admit that they're
suitable guinea pigs
for the experiment,
Professor Carnivory.
Professor, what's it all about?
What's that crackpot
scientist up to?
Why ask the Professor, Trixie?
He's working with
these terrible men.
Nobody asked your opinion.
You'll be better off keeping
your mouth shut, that's all.
[CARNIVORY] I hope those
children will forgive me.
But I can do nothing
to save them...
...nothing at all.
[TRIXIE screams]
Oh! Stop pointing that at me!
[SOLDIER A]
Stop! Stop that tank!
[SOLDIERS scream]
I have one last knob to turn,
Professor Carnivory.
Watch very closely.
[yelps]
[SPEED gasps]
Speed! I'm very
glad you got here!
[TRIXIE]
Speed!
Perfect timing, Speed!
[SPEED]
Their soldiers are coming!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[SOLDIERS scream]
Come on, Speed! Help us
get down from this wall!
Oh, Speed, I don't know what we
would have done without you.
[SPEED]
Never mind that, Trixie.
I've got to get you out of here.
[TRIXIE]
You're wonderful, Speed.
Don't forget me!
I don't wanna stay here!
[LOON growls]
I'm not gonna let them get away.
I'm not gonna let them
ruin my experiment.
[CARNIVORY]
No, you don't!
[LOON yelps]
I'm your old friend.
Why are you betraying me?
I'm not your friend, Dr. Loon.
I couldn't be the friend of a
man who makes such a machine.
It's my duty to see that you
never threaten
the world with it.
[LOON]
Don't shoot!
[SMASHER] Your brave talk
is useless, Professor!
[CARNIVORY]
Huh?! General Smasher!
Keep away from me!
You're wasting your time
if you think you can
fight me and my men.
You have no choice
but to do as I command.
Help us build an army of giants
and help us take over
every country on Earth!
[SMASHER screams]
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
Chim Chim! You're some shot!
[BOTH laugh]
Trixie! Professor!
Get into the tank! Hurry up!
--[SPEED grunting]
--[SOLDIERS groaning]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Stop that tank!
You must stop them!
[SOLDIERS scream]
[LOON sobs]
Oh, my laboratory, it's ruined.
Twenty years of hard work,
and it's ruined completely!
[sobs]
[gorilla roars]
[roaring]
[roars]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
That monster! It's walking
toward the power room!
It's got to be stopped!
Stop the prisoners
from escaping!
And the rest of you,
stop that monster gorilla!
Oh, they're coming, Speed!
A whole fleet of tanks!
Take over the controls
of this tank, Trixie.
I'm gonna get the Mach 5.
They've almost caught up!
Nothing can stop that monster!
The power room is smashed.
The roof'll be
tumbling in any minute!
Men, hurry! Get out
while you can!
This place is about to blow up!
[SMASHER gasps]
[LOON crying]
[LOON]
Ruined! Ruined!
It's dangerous, Dr. Loon!
Come on, let's get out
of here while we can!
Come on!
But this means the end of my
beloved country which loves war!
[sobs]
But maybe, Doctor,
it's for the best.
Maybe we were wrong.
[gasps]
Trixie, Spritle, Professor,
come on! Hop in the Mach 5!
This is my special seat.
Come on, Chim Chim!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[CARNIVORY] Well, that's
the end of those men and
their evil plans to restore the
dreaded war country of Giltar.
Fortunately, they were
stopped before they could
involve too many innocent people
in their diabolical scheme.
And now, they've been punished.
I'm sorry that you were put
to so much trouble, Speed.
If we hadn't met in that plane,
none of this would've happened.
And you would be in Nairobi
for the start of the
Trans-Africa Race.
[SPEED] What are you
gonna do now, Professor?
[CARNIVORY]
I'll go back to that island and
return those animals and
insects to their normal size.
You can still get to
the starting point
of that race in time.
[SPEED]
Mm-hmm!
Come on, Spritle. Let's get back
to Nairobi for the race.
I'm ready.
[NARRATOR]
Don't miss the next
exciting episode
of... Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪