♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[SPEED] We were on
our way to Sandoland
for the big Desert Race,
but little did Trixie
or Sparky or I know
just what we were getting into.
[SPEED] It began when a car
called the Black Tiger
owned by Kim of Flathill
Country was blown up.
This slingshot was in the car.
It's evidence that
you, Speed Racer,
ordered your little brother
to blow up the Black Tiger.
[SPEED] But Spritle had
seen a one-eyed man
plant a time bomb in Kim's car.
So, we drove across
the desert in the Mach 5
toward Flathill Country
where I could tell Kim
that we weren't the ones
who had blown up his car.
[SPEED] We were captured by
an army of Flathill rebels
and taken to their fortress.
To our surprise,
Kim turned out to be the son of
the general leading the rebels
and he didn't believe
that we were innocent.
The one-eyed man,
Ali Ben Schemer,
ordered the soldiers
to burn the Mach 5,
and we stood by as it
was enveloped by flame.
[SPRITLE]
Oh, the Mach 5 is gonna burn up!
[SPEED]
There's nothing we can do!
[ALL gasp]
[yells]
[TRIXIE]
Speed! Run!
[SPRITLE]
Look out, Speed!
[MAN]
Stop!
The one who blew up your car
was my cousin, Ali Ben Schemer.
Ali Ben Schemer.
[SPRITLE]
You see?
None of us had anything to
do with blowing the car up.
Ben Schemer, are you guilty?
Why did you destroy my chances
of winning the Desert Race?!
Wait, Kim. I gave him
orders to blow up your car.
Forgive me, but you were
so anxious to enter the race
that you didn't join our rebel
forces, and we needed you.
So that's it, eh? The only way
you could get me to join you
was to blow up my car so
I wouldn't be able to race.
[MAN] Strangers, I'm sorry that
my scheme with Ali Ben Schemer
caused you so much trouble,
but we are engaged in a
revolution against Flathill.
It is our old country,
and we love it,
but the government is
being run by criminals.
The only way to get them out
is to fight against them
with every means and
weapon we can gather.
If we succeed, our
country will then be run
by men of peace and goodwill.
Kim, now you know
I wasn't lying.
Yes, and it's too bad
they did that to my car.
[SPEED]
You would've have lost anyway.
[BEN SCHEMER]
Maybe not.
Who knows for sure which of you
would've won the Desert Race.
The only way to find out
is for the Black Tiger
to race against the Mach 5.
I'll get your car, the Black
Tiger, repaired right away.
[KIM] Hmm... You can
repair most of the car,
but the special brakes
can never be fixed.
Then I have a solution
to make you both equal.
The Mach 5 won't
have any either.
[SPEED]
Huh?
How could you stop
with no brakes?
Want to race with no brakes?
It'll be dangerous, but I'll try
it if you're willing to, Kim.
[TRIXIE]
No, Speed!
Don't worry, I'll be all right.
And it'll be good practice for
the big Desert Race, Trixie.
Let's make arrangements. You'll
race at dawn tomorrow morning.
The course will be around
the Palace of Doom.
[chuckles]
[engines revving]
It'll be night time by the
time you finish the race,
so you'd better take this lunch
with you. I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you, Ali.
Be careful and good luck!
Do your best to win, Speed!
This'll be the last
race for both of them.
They're in for a big surprise,
and they'll get it soon.
Now let's take care
of the rest of them.
Take them prisoner!
[gasps]
How dare you!
[SPRITLE growls]
Oh, put me down! Put me down!
[gibbering]
Ali Ben Schemer, what're
you doing to our visitors?
Have you gone wacky?
No, General Ali Gallant
I've become smarter!
What do you mean?
Uh! What's the meaning of this,
Ben Schemer? What's going on?!
[BEN SCHEMER]
From now on, General Gallant,
you'll no longer control
the Flathill Army.
From now on, I'm in command!
Are you rebels
rebelling against me?
That's the most accurate
way of putting it.
As commander of the rebel army,
I will take over all
of Flathill Country
and become its new king.
[GALLANT] No, I won't let you!
You will ruin Flathill if
you take it over for your own
selfish purposes! You can't!
[GALLANT gasps]
[GALLANT screaming]
[BEN SCHEMER chuckles]
[SPRITLE]
Chim Chim, help me!
Get the brats!
Let them go!
They won't last very long
out on that blazing desert
without any food or water.
That'll be the end of them.
I hope he finds Speed and
tells him what happened...
[SPEED] This desert is hot...
It's blazing hot...
But I've got to win.
I've got to beat Kim.
[gasps]
There's a scorpion
on you! Don't move!
[whimpering]
Remember, if you make a move,
it'll sting you
and that'll be it.
Get ready to jump
out of your car.
I've got one of them
in here with me.
I'll jump at the same time;
let's start slowing down.
[KIM]
Jump!
[SPEED] There. That takes
care of the scorpions.
If we'd been stung, that
would've been the end.
You know, they were
planted in our car.
When we get back,
I'm going to investigate.
Now, let's start up again.
The race isn't over yet,
and I'm going to beat you.
Oh yeah?
There seems to be no end
to it, and the sun's hot.
And I'm thirsty. Aren't you
thirsty, too, Chim Chim?
Hmm? But there's
no water anywhere.
Oh!
The camel's engine ran out of
water, but we've got to go on.
Camel, this is no place
to spend a summer vacation.
Ah!
[SPRITLE]
Huh...? Oh...
[VULTURES screeching]
[SPRITLE] Huh...? An oasis...
There must be water there.
[screams]
Huh?!
[SPRITLE]
Hmm?!
It's nothing but a mirage!
[VULTURES sceeching]
[gunshots]
[LEADER] It's a small boy
and a chimpanzee.
I wonder how long they
have been out here
in the middle of
the blazing desert.
Give them water, quickly!
[SPRITLE gasps]
Are you feeling better now? Hmm?
[SPRITLE] Who are you?
Where'd you come from?
We are soldiers in the
Flathill Government Army.
That must mean
that you're looking
for the Flathill rebel
soldiers, isn't that right?
That's right, we are.
Oh, then please!
You've got to help me!
I've got to find my
brother and Kim,
and I've got to find them
before it's too late!
Huh?!
[KIM] Speed! I'm caught
in quicksand! Help me!
[BOTH gasping]
[SPEED]
We're almost out! Come on!
[KIM gasps]
[SPEED]
I can't get us out!
Pull!
[CHIM CHIM gibbering]
Keep pulling!
[gasps]
[KIM] Y-You are General Abdul
Noble... of the Government Army.
Kim, while you were
racing in the desert,
Ali Ben Schemer took
over the rebel army
and got rid of your father.
[KIM]
Huh?
[laughing]
You've made that up.
I don't believe a word of it.
[SPEED] Kim, General
Abdul Noble's not lying.
[KIM]
Huh?!
Spritle and Chim Chim
just made a narrow escape
from Ali Ben Schemer.
He put those scorpions
in our lunch bags.
He doesn't want us stopping him
from taking over
Flathill Country.
And Chim Chim and
I saw the whole thing
when General Ali Ben Schemer
got rid of your father.
[GALLANT] We're sorry to give
you all this bad news, Kim.
Trixie wasn't able to get
away when Chim Chim and I
made our break for it,
so they captured her.
Huh?
We must rescue her.
[KIM]
Mm-hmm.
We'll work together.
Speed, if I trusted you
right from the beginning,
none of this would've happened.
But now, let's both
try to rescue Trixie
and overcome Schemer.
[SPEED] All right, Kim,
we'll be friends.
[CAMEL bellowing]
[TRIXIE]
Speed, oh, Speed, where are you?
[knocking]
[gasps]
[TRIXIE]
Who's there?!
Who is it? Can you hear me?
[VOICE]
Yes, I'm Prince Omar.
Prince Omar of Flathill?
My name's Trixie
and I'm a prisoner.
[OMAR]
So am I, Trixie.
The rebels captured
me and took me away
from my beloved country.
Tomorrow morning, they
will get rid of me forever.
You have a lovely voice.
I wish we could meet before...
...before tomorrow...
[gasps]
You still have a few hours,
so let's hope my
boyfriend Speed Racer
can rescue us before morning.
Halt!
Who are you? What do you want?
[KIM] Ali of Mim's my name,
and I'm here to sell fruit.
Huh?!
Let me see you!
[KIM]
I...
[SPRITLE]
Uh-oh...
Let them.
Halt!
[KIM] Oh? You changed your mind?
You'd like some fruit?
[gasps]
[whimpering]
They're delicious fruit.
All right, I'll buy one.
[KIM]
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm!
Coming up!
Ohh... Thanks, pal!
Huh?! Hold it!
[yells]
Now we rescue the prisoners!
To the basement!
I'm with you, Kim! Come on!
Help! We're being attacked!
What happened to Speed?
[KIM]
Shh!
We're on the same
side now, Trixie,
and I'm here to get you
out of this fortress.
Prince Omar's a prisoner here,
too! Help him get away!
[KIM]
His Highness is here?
There's one more thing I've got
to do before we leave here.
General Ali Ben Schemer lied
saying that Flathill was being
governed by crooks who
should be overthrown.
He just wanted to take over
the country for himself.
Now I'll burn all of
Ben Schemer's supplies.
[BEN SCHEMER]
Oh, no you won't, Kim!
Because now, you're finished!
[KIM]
You're finished, Ben Schemer!
This is the end of your
scheme, and it failed!
Right now,
the Flathill Government
Army is on its way here
to take over this fortress.
Let them try; this
place is invicible!
They'll be destroyed
if they try!
Ha, ha, ha! And then,
Flathill Country will be mine!
[SOLDIER C]
Lower the gate!
[gasps]
Hurry, Spritle!
We're coming, Speed!
We're coming!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[BEN SCHEMER]
I took the precaution
of having the fortress
surrounded by a huge pit
concealed under the sand, and
now the Flathill Government Army
has fallen into the
special sand trap,
and you'll fall in if
you try to get away!
Ah!
[BOTH gasp]
[screams]
They're coming out now!
[REBELS yelling]
[SPRITLE gasps]
[BEN SCHEMER]
Stop them!
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentleman,
the great Desert Race
is about to begin.
Unfortunately, one of
the possible winners,
Kim of Flathill Country,
is unable to compete due to his
car being lost in quicksand.
But Speed Racer has
joined the lineup,
and in his Mach 5, is one
of the top contenders.
[KIM] Good luck, Speed.
Win the race for me.
You can count on me.
I'll try to do my best, Kim.
[KIM]
Thank you.
[ANNOUNCER]
Prince Omar is arriving.
[trumpets blare]
I've never seen the prince,
I've only spoken to him through
the wall in the fortress.
And now finally I'll see him.
[OMAR] My aids tell me
that you're the young lady
I spoke to through
the fortress wall
when we were in prison together.
Now, at last, I can see
your face and you're lovely...
Lovely...
[gasps]
There goes Speed,
pulling into the lead.
I'm sure he'll be the winner.
Come on!
--Come on, Speed!
--[SPRITLE] Go, Speed! Go!
[NARRATOR] Speed will easily
win the great Desert Race.
But what new, exciting
adventure lies just ahead?
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪