♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[STEWARDESS] Attention, please.
Attention, please.
We will be landing
in a few minutes
at the airport in Hong Kong.
Ahh...
I can almost see it.
[TRIXIE]
Ohh...
[SPEED gasps]
[grunts]
[SPEED]
What's the matter?
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
It's too late. He was
poisoned by this needle.
She fired it!
Young lady, I want you
to give me your compact.
Huh?
[SPEED gasps]
She was hit by a needle.
The same as the man was.
[SPRITLE, CHIM CHIM gasp]
[SPRITLE]
What's this?
[SPEED]
Hmm? Where'd you find this card?
[SPRITLE]
Right here, Speed!
Part of it was sticking
out of her pocket book,
so I took it all the way out!
This is an invitation
to one of Hong Kong's
famous floating restaurants!
[REPORTERS shouting]
Mr. Racer, I'd like to
ask you a few questions,
--if you don't mind!
--I'm from a rival newspaper,
and I'd like to know what
you think your chances are
of winning the Hong Kong
International Race!
I'm from the Hong Kong
Automotive News!
Tell me all about the Mach 5!
Well, I think they're unloading
it right this minute.
That car, the Mach 5, was
designed and built by my father.
[REPORTER 1]
Go on, Speed!
Here comes Princess
Peddle's jet plane!
[SPEED]
Huh...
They've gone! All the reporters
just ran over there.
One of them said that's Princess
Peddle's special jet plane.
They ran over to see her.
I've never heard of her. Do you
know who Princess Peddle is?
She's a mysterious princess
who comes from the
Kingdom of Blastinbow.
I overheard someone talking
about her on the plane.
They said she's returning
from a world tour.
[SPEED] Where's the
Kingdom of Blastinbow?
Well, I'm not sure
exactly where it is,
but it's somewhere
in the Middle East.
I also heard that the princess
is one of the richest
girls in the whole world
because of all the oil
produced by her country.
That explains why
she has enough money
to travel around the world
in her own private plane.
She's very pretty and she's
about your age, Trixie,
but she's very elegant.
That's a fine thing to say!
You don't think I'm elegant?!
Aw, I didn't mean it.
Why'd you stop me?
It's the wrong time.
There's too much danger.
[ASSASSIN]
Oh. What do you mean?
[STEWARDESS] Agent 6 took
care of the secret agent
of the Blastinbow secret police
while we were on the plane.
But someone saw her do the job,
so I had to take care of her.
Otherwise, if she had been
arrested, she might've talked.
Who was the one who
saw her do the job?
Speed Racer.
Speed Racer...
I've heard of him.
He was flying here for the
Hong Kong International Race.
I'm afraid we're going to
have to keep an eye on him.
This is the famous ferry
boat that goes between
Hong Kong Island and the Kowloon
Peninsula across the harbor.
It's great that you can
take the Mach 5 along.
We're almost there. We're
almost at Hong Kong Island.
The buildings look
beautiful against the sky.
Well, you'll find that there
are many beautiful buildings
in Hong Kong.
Hey, look at the boat!
[ferry horn blares]
Look over to the right.
That's called Victoria Peak.
--[gunshot]
--[FERRYMAN grunts]
[SPEED gasps]
[gasps]
[TRIXIE screams]
I missed Speed!
--[SPRITLE gasps]
--Look how fast that boat moves!
[SPEED] Too fast...
The shot came from that boat...
[HOTEL CLERK]
Room 707, Mr. Racer.
It has a beautiful
view of the harbor.
[SPRITLE]
Wow... What a fabulous hotel!
Look at those Chinese lanterns!
Everything's so clean and
neat and Oriental. Wow.
I love it! What a place,
huh, Chim Chim?
Speed...
Huh?
He's right.
Can we really afford to stay
at such a fabulous hotel?
It must cost a lot
of money for a room.
Well, Trixie, if I win the race,
we won't have to
worry about money.
[TRIXIE] But you can't
be sure of winning!
[SPEED] It's not every day
we get into a fabulous city
like this, so let's
enjoy it and not worry.
Let me go, let me go,
let me go! Cut that out!
Agent 9 reporting.
They're occupying room 707.
I'll continue to
keep watching them.
[TRIXIE]
Hmm...
[SPEED]
What is it, Trixie?
[TRIXIE]
The water looks so beautiful!
The view from this window
is like a beautiful dream.
I can see the whole harbor.
[CHIM CHIM gibbering]
[SPRITLE laughing]
Let me see...
Huh?
There were those murders
on the plane when the girl
who fired the needle at that
man was taken care of herself,
and then that ferryboat captain
was shot right in front of me.
It's strange. I can't figure out
what the connection can be.
[TRIXIE] Well, neither can I,
but I'm sure of one thing:
Those incidents had
nothing to do with us.
Wait a minute! Trixie, maybe
they weren't coincidences!
Maybe they were aiming at me!
[gasps]
The captain was
there by accident.
He was leaning in front of me
when he was hit by a bullet
fired from the boat
that sped away.
If he hadn't been
in front of me,
I would've been
hit by the bullet.
That's why I think someone
was deliberately trying
to get rid of me.
Now you must admit, it makes
a lot of sense, Trixie.
But why, Speed?
Why did they do it?
I wish I knew the answer...
The only reason
I'm able to figure out
is that I happened
to be a witness
to the first murder
on that plane.
And so, because I
knew that girl did it,
they got rid of the girl, too.
The one who got rid of her
had to be someone on that plane,
someone who knew that
I had been a witness.
And whoever it is is afraid
of me because of what I know,
and they feel they've gotta
get me outta the way.
[SPEED] That has to be the
only reason someone's after me.
I've gotta find
out who they are.
Trixie, why don't we go out?
Oh, that's what we've
been waiting for!
Let's all go out!
You'd better stay right here
in the room. It'll be safer!
[SPRITLE, CHIM CHIM groan]
[TRIXIE] Since we're here,
let's not travel in the Mach 5,
let's use the Hong Kong
method of travel.
What's the Hong Kong
method of travel?
Well, isn't this
much more romantic
than traveling in the Mach 5?
[SPEED]
Hmm.
[TRIXIE] By the way, Speed,
where are we going?
To visit the
floating restaurant.
[TRIXIE]
Oh! The floating restaurant?
[SPEED] Don't you
remember the invitation
that woman who was murdered
on the plane had in her purse?
I never imagined that
a restaurant on a boat
could be so elegant.
Elegant enough for even an
elegant princess to visit.
[SPEED]
Ohh... Princess Peddle.
She's elegant, all right.
[TRIXIE]
Hmph!
Those swords she's
dancing with are real
and look very sharp.
Speed!
[TRIXIE]
She's much too elegant.
Ouch!
[gasps]
[SPEED]
Huh?
[gasps]
I missed again!
[SPEED]
Wait! Wait!
[gasps]
[SPEED]
Wait!
A strange kind of weapon.
One I've never seen before.
And the people on the plane
were hit by poison needles.
There must be some connection.
And whoever invented these
weapons is very clever.
[TRIXIE]
Speed! Speed!
Speed, I have a message for you!
[SPEED]
Huh?
Princess Peddle sent word that
she wants to see you right now!
I'm to see Princess Peddle, hmm?
[SPEED] Now maybe some of the
missing parts of the mystery
will fall into place...
Thank you for saving
my life, Speed.
It was really an honor, Princess
Peddle. I'm glad I could help.
[PEDDLE] And I'm glad to
hear you say that, Speed,
because I'm afraid I
need your help again.
Huh?
[PEDDLE]
That's right.
Because I'm a princess and
the richest girl in the world,
there're people trying
to get me out of the way
so they can take my
throne and money.
So someone's trying to
get rid of the princess?
And she wants you
to be her bodyguard?
But, Speed, you're
liable to be hurt!
[SPEED]
Hmm...
It could be dangerous,
but what else could I do?
She said it would cause
an international scandal
if she went to the
Hong Kong police
and asked them to protect her.
And she can't run away because
that would seem suspicious.
[TRIXIE]
Did you agree to take the job?
[SPEED]
Yes.
But you know you've got
a race coming up soon!
[SPEED] The Hong Kong Grand
Prix! And I'm gonna win it!
Well, we might as well
make the most of things.
The princess has to do
some sightseeing today,
but I have an idea.
[AGENT 9]
So far, they're safe.
[SPEED] And on your
right... [clears throat]
[rasping voice] On your
right, Princess Peddle,
is a statue of
Prince Whosamawhatsits,
and his, uh, pet
pig Snortaporcine,
and his mother, Queen Zizi.
These statues have been here
for at least a thousand years!
[SPEED]
How am I doing, Trixie?
[TRIXIE]
Just great! Keep it up, Speed.
[SPEED]
Okay.
[rasping voice]
Uh, these statues represent
the characters in
an ancient legend.
I wish I'd read up on
it before we came here,
so I could tell you more about
it, but there wasn't time.
[SPEED]
Look out!
[TRIXIE gasps]
[ASSASSIN]
Huh?!
That's Speed! It was
a trap! Come on!
[SPEED]
Wait!
Stop! Come back here!
Come back here!
[engine revs]
There she goes. I'll try to
catch her with the Mach 5.
[gasps]
[ASSASSIN]
I can't let him catch me!
[gasps]
That's poison gas!
[SPEED]
Oil!
[gasping]
I wonder what else
she'll try to pull.
[SPEED] You weren't hurt.
Come on, get up!
[ASSASSIN]
Huh?
You heard me. Stop faking.
Come on, get up!
I'm not taking orders from you!
You're taking them from me!
[SPEED]
Huh?
Even though you've got a gun,
it's not gonna help you!
I'm taking you back to the city
and turning you
over to the police!
[gunshot]
[ASSASSIN gasps]
[SPEED]
Huh?
Mr. Racer, thank you
very much for helping us.
I'm from the International
Police Department.
This woman is a
member of the ring
that wants to get rid of
Princess Peddle and her family.
I'm placing you under arrest
and we're going to round up
the rest of your murderous gang.
Are you? That's what you think!
You haven't met up with X yet!
Just wait till you meet X!
[SPEED] X? I wonder who
that mysterious X is...
You look worried, Speed.
[SPRITLE]
Better snap out of it, Speedy!
The race is going to begin soon,
and you've gotta
concentrate on driving.
[TRIXIE]
Look at all the spectators!
A lot of them are here
to see you win, Speed.
You don't wanna disappoint them.
Are you all right? You're acting
as if something's the matter.
Am I? I'm worried
about the princess.
Look, there's Princess
Peddle up there!
[SPEED]
She's still in danger,
but how am I going to protect
her and race at the same time?
Wow!
Ha...
[SPRITLE] Wow! I didn't know
there'd be a woman racer!
[ANNOUNCER]
Start your engines!
[engines revving]
[SPEED] Princess Peddle is going
back to her own country tonight,
so now would be the last chance
for her enemies to get her.
I'll bet they try something
while this race is going on.
I hope he'll win.
He will! Nobody can beat
the Mach 5 with Speed driving!
Hey, wait a minute! Something's
funny about that woman!
[SPEED] The International
Police didn't get
the leader of the gang,
so he must be around.
[SPEED] So far, the members of
that gang seem to be women,
and I've seen that woman
racer somewhere before...
...but where?
Ah! She's the stewardess
from that plane!
She must be the ringleader,
the mysterious X!
She's staying back there.
She must have a reason and
I've gotta find out what it is
and try to stop her!
So that's her plan!
I've gotta do something fast!
Ah!
What's Speed doing?!
I wonder why he's
pulling off the course!
[gasps]
Speed, you've beaten me!
My scheme failed!
You're X! Don't deny it!
You're the leader of the gang
that tried to get
Princess Peddle!
Right! But you stopped me!
If you hadn't, I would've taken
over the princess's throne
and her vast fortune!
Her country would've been mine!
But now, I've got
nothing! I-I...
[X groaning]
[PEDDLE] She'll be all right.
She just fainted.
Thank you, Speed, for
saving my life again.
Well, I'm glad I did, Princess.
Now you'll be able to
return to your home safely.
[SPRITLE]
So long!
Now she won't have to worry.
The gang was arrested.
But the Hong Kong Grand Prix
is over. And Speed lost.
He didn't even have a
chance to finish the race.
Well, there was something
much more important.
I had to save Princess Peddle.
And I'll be racing again.
[NARRATOR]
Don't miss the next
exciting episode
of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪