♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR] A gang of assassins
suspects that one of the racers
on his way to the
Twist 'n' Turn Race in Abalonia
is a secret agent
for the police.
So the assassins plan
to get rid of him.
[tires screech]
[MUFFLE screams]
[tires screeching]
[explosion]
[NARRATOR]
The assassin gang suspects that
Speed also might be a secret
agent for the police.
And so, in the front left tire,
they set a bomb to go off
when the tire reaches
a certain temperature.
But Spritle warned
Speed by radio.
[SPEED grunting]
[SPEED]
Get down!
[SPEED] The story really
began when I drove to
the exotic and mysterious
city of Ambrocia
for one of the world's most
famous races,
the Mystic Grand Prix.
I didn't know it at the time,
but a gang of
assassins was planning
to take over the country
by getting rid
of its ruling monarchs,
Prince Snowier and
Princess Gracious.
As Their Highnesses stood on
their balcony for the race,
an assassin was taking aim.
But one of the racers in
the race-- no one knows who--
was a secret agent,
and he flashed a mirror
at the assassin,
spoiling his aim.
I spotted the assassin
and fought with him
on one of the rooftops,
high above the city.
[BOTH grunting, groaning]
[ASSASSIN screams]
[SPEED] The Mystic Grand Prix
was cancelled,
and so I left for
the Twist 'n' Turn Race
to be held in
the country of Abalonia.
The assassins thought I might be
the International Police
secret agent
who foiled the assassination,
so along the way,
they tried to get rid of me.
But I escaped them.
I also learned that now
the gang was trying to
take over the
country of Abalonia
by planting a time bomb in
the home of President Montebank.
I didn't have much time
left to try to save him.
[SPEED] Meanwhile,
at President Montebank's home,
the President was about
to welcome the racers
who already had arrived.
Time was running out.
[SPEED] I've got to get there
before that bomb goes off.
I've got to!
[applause]
[GUARD]
Hey! Your identification card!
[groans]
[MAN A]
Halt!
Hey! Who are you?
What do you want?!
[SPEED panting]
[MAN A]
Stop! [grunts]
[groans]
[MONTEBANK gasps]
[explosion]
[RACER X]
Speed!
Speed! Where are you? Speed!
The International Police are
making a complete investigation
into the assassination attempt.
They believe that
a gang of assassins
is out to assassinate
President Montebank
and take over Abalonia.
President Montebank's life
was saved by Speed Racer,
one of the competitors in the
upcoming Twist 'n' Turn Race.
Speed has been seriously hurt.
[NEWSCASTER]
The injured racer, Speed Racer,
is recuperating right now in a
room at the national hospital.
[VICE PRESIDENT]
Hmm...
Mr. Vice President? Here we are.
[ELEGANTOR] We're here to
visit President Montebank.
I'm sorry, but nobody's allowed
to see President Montebank.
What's the matter
with you, Doctor?
Don't you realize this
is Vice President Duper?
He must be allowed in
to see President Montebank.
The President's condition
is much too serious
for anyone to be permitted
inside, no matter who they are.
[ELEGANTOR] Hmm. So his
condition is very bad.
[DOCTOR]
I'm afraid so.
[ELEGANTOR]
Hmm, we'll leave him alone then.
But while I'm here,
I might as well pay a visit
to the other victim.
[TRIXIE]
Who's there?
[ELEGANTOR] A representative
of Vice President Duper.
This is a great honor, sir.
Thank you for coming.
You had a very close call.
How do you feel?
Better?
Oh, I'm feeling
much better, sir.
I'm even able to work this arm.
Excellent, Speed.
On behalf of
Vice President Duper,
I want to thank you
for saving the President
by risking your life.
Oh, thank you, sir.
I'm glad that I was
able to save him.
Please come to Vice President
Duper's home tomorrow.
I'll see you there.
[SPEED]
Yes, sir.
Thank you for the visit.
[TRIXIE]
Oh!
[SPRITLE]
You know something?
I don't like the
looks of that man.
[TRIXIE]
Now, Spritle!
He represents
the Vice President.
You mustn't talk
like that about him.
Oh, hello! Come on in, Racer X!
Hi, Racer X!
--Here, I brought some flowers.
--[TRIXIE sighs] Thanks.
[RACER X] And here's
something for you, Spritle.
Thanks, Racer X.
Speed, how are you?
Are you feeling all right?
[SPEED]
Uh-huh.
The doctor told him
he can go today.
I'm very glad to hear that.
And we were just invited
to pay a visit tomorrow
to Vice President Duper's home.
To visit the home of
Vice President Duper?
So the man who was
here was posing
as a Vice President's
representative.
Well, I sure am glad
to hear you're all right.
See you later.
[SPEED] When I mentioned going
to the Vice President's home,
Racer X changed.
Could he be a secret agent?
This is Number 9.
I'm calling Paris.
[buzzing]
Chief, Agent 9 is reporting.
This is the Chief.
Go ahead, Agent 9;
I'm listening.
[RACER X]
According what I've discovered,
the gang of assassins
will take over
the country of
Abalonia very soon.
But how can those
men possibly do it?
[RACER X]
I just found out that
one of the high government
officials is in with them.
What do you mean?
What's the man's name?
[RACER X]
Vice President Duper.
The Vice President?!
Are you sure of that, Racer X?
[RACER X] Well, sir,
he stands to become president
if President Montebank
doesn't pull through.
It's logical, isn't it?
[CHIEF]
Hmm...
Vice President Duper in
with the assassins, eh?
He probably hired them to
come and do his dirty work.
Unless this man and the
assassins can be stopped,
the country of
Abalonia's doomed.
Vice President Duper invited me.
Oh yes, Mr. Racer,
he's been expecting you.
If you'll follow me,
I'll lead the way.
That's strange.
Vice President Duper
lives underground?
[ELEGANTOR]
Well...
Ever since the bomb went off
at the President's house,
the Vice President is careful.
[SPEED]
I see.
I'm sorry, Mr. Racer,
but you'll have to wait here.
[ELEGANTOR] You stoneheads
blew the job once,
so I'm warning you...
You'd better not
blow it this time.
It's locked.
Now why'd he lock me in?
[knocking]
[SPRITLE]
Who's that?
[TRIXIE]
Coming.
Oh, Racer X!
Hi, I came to talk to Speed.
You can't; Speed's
not here right now.
Where is Speed?
He left a little while ago for
Vice President Duper's house.
I'm too late then, Trixie!
Racer X, is anything wrong?
[SPRITLE] Every time we see
Racer X, he leaves in a hurry.
I wonder what he's up to and
where he's going this time.
I wonder why he's running.
[knocking]
Sorry we kept you waiting.
Come this way.
[SPEED gasps]
Listen, you didn't
have to pull a gun!
I'm willing to go
wherever you say!
[ASSASSIN A]
Move.
The way you act, you have
something to hide, I'll bet.
[ASSASSIN A groans]
[BOTH grunting]
[SPEED gasps]
[BOTH chuckle]
[RACER X]
Speed's in danger.
I hope I can get to him in time.
[SPEED]
See you!
It's Speed Racer!
I heard that
Speed Racer's inside.
I wanna see him.
I'm sorry,
but he's left already.
Left already?
[RACER X] There's something
strange about that.
[cackles]
I find it hard to believe
that such an excellent
driver as Speed
drove his car right off
the road into the ocean.
Well, that's why we're
havin' the funeral.
It's very strange
and suspicious.
But it's a fact that he crashed.
There's no getting around that.
[door clicks]
[RACER X]
Huh?
Speed...
This funeral's for you.
I know, but I'm okay.
Get out of sight
before someone sees you.
Now tell me why you're letting
everyone think you crashed.
What's this
all about, Speed? Well?
I was trapped by
a gang of assassins,
who were trying to
take over this country.
They tried to get rid of me,
and if they think
they succeeded,
maybe I can find out
more about them.
Well, take my advice
and don't have anything more
to do with them.
I'm sure those men,
whoever they are, are dangerous.
After all, they tried
to get rid of the President.
And if you fall
into their hands again,
they'll make sure you won't
get away the next time.
I've gotta take the chance.
All right, if you feel that way,
then maybe the two of us
better work together
on the case to see that
those men are stopped.
Do you agree?
[SPEED]
Yes.
That man over there
is the leader.
[ASSASSIN B]
Hey, Boss.
I just heard that
President Montebank
is gonna make
a trip to La Mamba.
He must be better.
That's right, he's better.
So he's going to
La Mamba for a vacation.
I'm very glad to hear that.
[THUG A] This is Station 12;
Group A is ready, sir.
Our plans are completed
and everything's ready
to get rid of President
Montebank once and for all.
It won't be long before
you'll be appointed
the new president of Abalonia.
Gee, I'll be the
new president, thanks to you.
Don't forget it.
And once you are the president,
you will follow my orders.
Or else we'll get
rid of you permanently.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
This is Number 9.
I'm putting in a call to Paris.
[OPERATOR] This is International
Police Headquarters.
[RACER X] I'm following
everybody to La Mamba.
I'll carry out instructions.
President Montebank is
taking a walk in the garden.
He'll be back in a little while.
Would you wait here, please?
--[DUPER mumbles]
--Excuse me.
Mr. Vice President, what's your
opinion about agrarian reform?
Opinion about agrarian reform...
Well, I... Uh, I--
And how do you feel about a more
secure social security system?
[DUPER] Hmm... Well, I haven't
thought about it yet.
[ELEGANTOR coughs]
I'm going to get
some fresh air outside.
I'll be right back.
I'll give you
my opinion in a minute.
Listen, you stonehead.
Tell him you've thought about it
and you're all for it.
Make him think you've
got a brain in your head!
[DUPER]
Mm-hmm.
After careful consideration,
I'm for all kinds of reform.
Mm-hmm. Good.
[DUPER]
Yeah, aren't you?
I am.
I'll have to watch that
stonehead every minute
and tell him what he's
supposed to think all the time.
Group A, are you prepared?
[THUG A]
We're standing by.
Good. Now watch your step.
[RACER X]
Mm-hmm. They're getting ready.
I'm very impressed with your
opinions, Mr. Vice President.
You'd make a fine president
should anything permanent happen
to President Montebank.
I'm not so dumb.
Here comes the President back
from his stroll in the garden.
[DUPER]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[GUARDS scream]
[gunshots]
[NURSE gasps]
You're not fair! That hurt!
[DUPER gasps]
[SPEED]
Trixie!
Let's get 'em!
--[SPEED, TRIXIE grunting]
--[ASSASSINS groaning]
[SPEED yells]
[SPRITLE chuckles]
[SPEED]
Huh?
[SPRITLE gasps]
[SPEED gasps]
Now I've got him.
I'll finish him.
[chuckles]
Ah!
Uh-oh!
[ALL gasp]
[POLITICIAN]
I don't understand.
What's the meaning of this?
What happened to
President Montebank?
[SPEED]
Don't worry, sir.
President Montebank is
very safe somewhere else.
You see, this was all a trick
to catch the gang of assassins.
What?! I'm very glad
to hear about that.
[RACER X]
Vice President Duper,
we know you were
in on the whole plot.
What?! Who's talkin' in my ear?!
Well, you might call me
a fighter for justice.
The plot to assassinate
President Montebank
and take over Abalonia
is a complete flop.
And I'm taking the leader
of the gang to jail.
[groans]
[SPEED gasps]
--[SPEED] Look out!
--[tires screech]
Get in, Duper! Come on!
[SPEED]
I can't let them get away!
[gasps]
[ELEGANTOR]
Speed Racer's following us, eh?
This'll be a cinch.
[ELEGANTOR]
Now's our chance.
I'll use the oil.
[SPEED gasps]
I'll blast him.
[ELEGANTOR growls]
It's no use. Stop the car.
Let's give up to 'im.
Don't be chicken!
Listen, I'm a chicken
Vice President!
I know that!
[DUPER shouts]
[ELEGANTOR gasps]
--[car honking]
--[tires screeching]
[gasps]
[SPEED] Well, that's the end of
that terrible gang of assassins.
They tried to assassinate
Princess Gracious of Ambrocia,
and then President
Montebank of Abalonia.
But they failed both times.
It's the end of that gang.
But there will be others.
As long as men
seek power illegally,
there will be evil things
done in the world.
But I'll do all I can
to see that men like them
never succeed.
If everyone did the same, it
would be a more peaceful world.
[engines revving]
[ANNOUNCER]
It's a beautiful day
here in the
capital city of Abalonia,
where we're celebrating the
10th anniversary of our country
with the start of the
great Twist 'n' Turn Race!
The race is about to begin!
[RACER X]
Speed, listen to me.
We worked together to
get rid of those assassins,
but from now on, we're
professional racers again
and I'll do my best to win.
I'll try to beat you.
And I'll try to win!
[RACER X]
Good luck.
The President's coming into
his box to give the signal
for the race to begin.
[CROWD cheering]
[RACER X] In a race,
it's every man for himself.
[SPEED] If he hadn't helped me,
I wouldn't be here today.
But a race belongs
to the best racer.
And I've gotta prove it's me.
[NARRATOR] More thrills,
more adventures lie ahead.
Don't miss the next exciting
episode of... Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪