♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[SPEED] I was in Japan
for the Fujiyama Grand Prix,
when a gang of
assassins were there
to get rid of all the
ministers from other countries
who had come to attend
the International
Piecemeal Conference.
I followed
the gang of assassins,
but they trapped me inside
an old Oriental castle.
Some strange statues of
ancient kings had me cornered.
[gasps]
[SPEED] They must be under
some kind of remote control.
But who's operating it?
And where are they?
I've got to find out.
[gasps]
[SPEED]
Oh!
[SPEED gasps]
[SPEED] So you're a gang
of assassins, huh?
Okay, come on!
[ASSASSIN A]
You're too nosy, kid.
And now, you know too much.
[SPEED, ASSASSIN grunt]
[yells]
[grunting]
[SPEED gasps]
[growls]
[gasps]
[ASSASSINS grunting]
[ASSASSINS groaning]
[SPEED gasps]
You're a tough kid all right,
but you don't have a chance.
--[gunshots]
--[gasps]
[GUNSEL laughs]
You're brave,
but you're very young yet.
[SPEED] You must be
the leader of these...
...th-these assassins!
Gaff Gunsel's my name,
and I'm the leader of this
division of assassins.
But our organization
is worldwide.
You shoulda kept away from us,
but now we've gotta
get rid of you
so you don't tell the police
what you've learned.
Walk over to that statue.
[SPEED gasps]
[ASSASSIN B]
Go on!
Okay, we'll go ahead. But you go
back and take care of his car.
[ASSASSIN B]
Yes, sir.
[DIPLOMAT A]
Let us out of here!
[DIPLOMAT B]
We're diplomats!
You can't keep us locked up!
My country will be angry when
they hear what you've done!
[GUNSEL]
Quiet!
We took these diplomats
off a sightseeing boat.
It's part of our plan.
If we get rid of all
the officials and diplomats
of every country, the world'll
be ours for the takin'!
Hey! You have right to keep
important men like us prisoners!
We came to this
country to participate
in the Piecemeal Conference!
It's important for world peace
that we be there!
Mm-mm. You're wasting
your breath.
They don't want us
to be at the conference.
[ASSASSIN C]
Good. Next!
[SPEED gasps]
[ASSASSIN D] We'll show you
what else we can do.
Watch.
[yells]
[GUNSEL] Now I'll show you
what kind of drivers
the assassins are.
[SPEED gasps]
[GUNSEL] They've mastered
how to overcome
every kind of driving obstacle
at whatever speed
they may be traveling.
There isn't a vehicle or
a person that can stop 'em.
And every car is equipped
to cope with every emergency.
They're all rolling
highly specialized weapons.
Now that you've seen a
demonstration of our potential,
I'm taking you to the top man
of all the assassins.
[ANARCHY]
You're a very clever young man.
You're brave and you're tough.
You can fight and you're
an excellent driver.
I'll give you a choice:
Either join us... or die.
[GUNSEL]
Oh, you hear that?!
Professor Anarchy is
offering you a great honor!
Well, don't keep him waiting;
give him your answer.
[SPEED laughs]
I won't join.
You made your decision
and I won't offer you
the choice again.
Get rid of him.
[GUNSEL groans]
[ANARCHY]
Don't move!
Drop the gun and get over there.
[SPEED grunts]
In a way, you're lucky because
you're going to have me
put a bullet through you.
You should feel flattered.
You'll be the 2,708th man
I've so honored.
[chuckles]
--[RACER X] Wait a minute.
--[ANARCHY] Hmm?!
[gasps] Racer X!
What are you doing here?
Save yourself the trouble,
Professor Anarchy.
I'll take care of the kid.
What's that?
Don't tell me you're a member
of the assassin gang.
Well, I am.
I'm not a full-fledged member
of the Worldwide Assassins.
Are you surprised?
You see, I was sick
and tired of racing
where I risk my neck for a few
dollars and a lot of glory.
I'll get more here.
[SPEED] And I thought you
were decent! You're rotten!
I advised you not to try to find
out more about the assassins.
Don't you remember?
But you wouldn't listen to me.
Too bad you didn't.
[ANARCHY]
Why waste time talking, Racer X?
Get to work on him.
All right, Boss.
[SPEED groans]
[RACER X] Sorry to have to do
this to you, Speed. I truly am.
[SPEED groans]
Oh, look at him! The poor boy!
Obviously someone did
a job on him!
Let us out of here, you fiend!
Go ahead, open up!
Save your breaths.
Nobody gets outta there unless
Professor Anarchy himself
gives the word,
and he's not givin' the word.
He'll be all right.
[DIPLOMAT C]
Let's hope so.
[SPEED groans]
I shouldn't have
trusted Racer X.
I thought he'd help.
Someday I'll find a way
to get even with all of them.
A nap will do him good.
[TRIXIE] Speed should never have
gone after those assassins!
He must've walked into
some kind of trap,
otherwise, he'd be back by now!
If only Speed would
use the homing robot
to tell us where he is.
[SPRITLE]
Speed!
[echoing] Speed! Speed!
[TRIXIE]
Speed!
Hey, Speed!
[TRIXIE echoing]
Speed!
[SPRITLE echoing]
Hey, Speed!
[TRIXIE echoing]
Speed!
[SPRITLE echoing]
Hey, Speed!
[TRIXIE echoing]
Speed!
[SPRITLE echoing]
Hey, Speed!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[BOTH gasp]
[SPRITLE] The homing robot
from Speed's car.
The homing robot must be
bringing a message from Speed.
Let's hope so.
It's headed that way!
Come on, let's try to catch it!
Okay!
[BOY A]
What a fabulous car.
[BOY B] I'll bet it goes
faster than fast.
[BOY C] How do you start it?
What are all those buttons for?
I'll press this one marked "D."
I wonder what'll happen now.
[BOY B] Hey, that
robot bird's comin' back.
[BOY C]
Yeah, it knows where to come!
[BOY B] It flies better
than a fly or a bird!
It popped right in! Amazing!
[TRIXIE]
Where's Speed?
[BOY C]
Who?
Speed Racer, the one
who owns this car.
[BOY B]
Speed Racer?
That's the Mach 5
and it belongs to him.
We don't know him
and this car belongs to us.
That's what you think.
You must've stolen the car.
[BOY A] Oh, yeah? We found that
car, so don't say we stole it.
It doesn't belong
to you, Shorty.
What do you mean by that?!
[TRIXIE] Spritle, this is
no time to get into a fight.
If Speed's in trouble,
we've got to find him
as fast as possible!
Now, come on.
Let us use the car and I'll give
you all the candy in my pocket.
[BOY A]
Candy?
[BOY B]
[BOYS]
Take the car!
Chim Chim, give them your candy.
[TRIXIE]
Hurry, Spritle!
[BOYS gasp]
That sightseeing boat
was attacked by a monster.
But maybe it wasn't
a real monster.
Maybe it was some
kind of submarine.
Is that why we're at
the bottom of the lake?
[TRIXIE]
Yes.
If that was a submarine
in disguise,
maybe if we can find it,
we can find Speed!
[BOTH laugh]
[CHIM CHIM, SPRITLE
gasp, scream]
[TRIXIE screams]
[BOTH gasping]
[SPRITLE]
Hurry, Trixie!
Hurry, it'll smash the car!
Faster!
[screams]
Come on, Trixie, hurry!
Get us out of here!
Come on!
That monster submarine's
drawing us up.
It's much too powerful!
[screams]
[SPRITLE] You were right,
Trixie. It is a submarine!
And this is what sank
the sightseeing boat
with all the diplomats on board.
And that means it belongs to
the men Speed
went to investigate.
[TRIXIE] So we may
be on the right road
to find Speed after all!
[SPRITLE] Shh! I think
I hear someone coming.
[footsteps]
[gasps]
There's somebody right outside!
They shouldn't
catch us together.
Open the cockpit.
I'll come to help you later.
Just pretend
that you're all alone.
Open the trunk. Hurry!
You must belong
to the assassins!
You're right. We're members
of Worldwide Assassins.
And we've been looking
for this car.
I'm glad you found it.
Now, get out of it!
Why should I?
What are you planning
to do with the car?
Ask all the questions you want,
but I won't answer.
Now get out!
What a peculiar place.
This must be the assassins'
main headquarters.
Why have you brought me here?!
Put her in the cell with
the rest of the prisoners.
And put that car she came in
in the storeroom!
[ASSASSIN E]
Okay, get in!
[SPEED]
Huh...?
[TRIXIE gasps]
[gasps] Trixie!
[TRIXIE]
Speed!
How were you captured?
Oh, Speed, never mind that!
At least I found you!
I searched all over!
[SPEED]
Hmm. I wouldn't be here myself
if I hadn't walked right
into the assassin's trap.
They're clever.
By the way, Trixie,
I found out that Racer X
is part of the gang.
He admitted it to me
just before he beat me up.
What?! Racer X
really beat you up?
Those are terrible men who are
keeping us prisoners here.
[DIPLOMAT D]
Oh... They've promised us
that they'll never let us go.
Unless we're rescued,
we'll never see our homes again.
Don't feel so badly.
There's still hope.
We still have a chance
at being rescued.
[DIPLOMAT E]
Really?
Are you saying that
just to cheer us up?
Listen, Speed,
Spritle and Chim Chim
are hiding in the trunk
of the Mach 5
waiting for a chance to help us.
I hope they get that chance.
The International
Piecemeal Conference
is scheduled to take place
at 10:00 tomorrow morning.
It's the opportunity
I've been waiting for.
Presidents and important
ministers from all
over the world will be assembled
in one place at that time.
And it'll be
the perfect time
for us to get rid of
all of them at once.
In the meeting hall
is the statue of a lion.
Tomorrow morning, it'll have
a powerful bomb inside it.
This lion statue I have here
looks exactly like
the one where the
meeting will take place,
except this one has
the bomb inside it,
set to go off at one minute
after 10 tomorrow morning.
Your mission is to get
inside the conference hall
and replace that lion statue
with this one
containing the bomb.
You must be very careful
how you handle it,
as any sudden bump
could set it off
and blow you and
the conference room sky high.
Let me show you where
the bomb is located.
I'm sure that they
have a heavy guard
around that conference hall
and will take every precaution
to see that nothing goes wrong.
But that shouldn't stop you.
If anyone challenges you or gets
in your way, get rid of him!
Do not hesitate to use your
weapons and be ruthless.
Your mission is of the utmost
importance, don't forget.
Now get going and good luck.
[ASSASSIN F]
We're ready!
[RACER X]
Professor Anarchy.
I have something
important to ask.
Go ahead.
Let me take charge
of the entire mission.
I give you my word,
I will not fail on it.
I'm glad to hear that you're
so conscientious, Racer X,
but I have another special
mission specially for you.
Our regular men can take of
the bomb planting job.
--Please let me!
--[ANARCHY] Mm-mmm.
You heard me.
Get going!
I hope they're successful.
Now for the next job.
Take the prisoners out of
the cell and line them up.
Right!
[SPEED grunting]
I wonder what Spritle's doing.
[SPRITLE grunting]
Locked. Maybe I could
use the homing robot.
[gasps] Racer X!
Here, Racer X.
You use the gun on 'em.
It's the same as shootin'
at clay pigeons.
Aim carefully. I don't
want you to miss one of them.
Show me just how good
a shot you are.
It's a pretty good gun,
Professor.
Now you'll see what
a perfect shot I am.
He's about to pull the trigger!
Ready? When I count to three,
you start shooting.
One...
[TRIXIE gasps]
Two...
[GUNSEL]
Three!
[chuckles]
[TRIXIE, SPEED gasp]
He... shot our ropes off!
[BOTH gasp]
[RACER X chuckles]
It took perfect shooting
to cut those ropes off.
You double-crossed us!
You're a traitor!
The only reason I joined
your organization
was so that I could
stop you from doing
what you're trying to do!
And that's why he beat me up, so
they would think he was loyal.
He was only trying
to trick them!
Who are you, Racer X?
An FBI agent?!
Take off your mask!
Show us your face so we know
who you really are!
You'll never find out.
Now radio your army of men
to come back here right away.
[laughs]
Look over there!
[RACER X]
Huh?
[ASSASSINS groaning]
[SPEED]
Come on!
[ASSASSINS groan]
Racer X, thanks for
everything you've done.
Save it. Thank me later.
Some assassins are on their way
to plant a bomb at
the conference.
You try to stop them.
[SPEED]
Right!
[ASSASSINS scream, groan]
Huh?!
Ahh, the Mach 5!
And just when we need it!
[TRIXIE]
Good job, Spritle!
[SPRITLE]
See, Speed?
[SPEED]
See what?
You didn't want me
to come along,
but now you're glad I did!
I'll see you later, Racer X.
[RACER X]
Good luck!
[TRIXIE gasps]
Professor, that boy
is getting away!
After him, quickly!
They're going after Speed!
Come on!
[SPRITLE gasps]
[RACER X]
Now's your chance to escape.
Open that door over there and
run straight down the corridor.
It'll lead you to safety.
--[DIPLOMATS murmuring]
--Go on! Run!
Ready the submarine.
[ASSASSIN G]
Yes, sir.
Come on!
[yelps]
They're getting away!
[RACER X]
Hmm...
There're enough guns
and ammunition here
to take over every
country on Earth!
Oh! This is a time bomb...
A time bomb is just what I need
to blow up this place
so nobody'll be able
to use it again.
I'll set the timer
for it to go off.
[timer ticking]
Huh?!
Someone's taking our cars!
Quick, cut him off!
[tires screech]
[SPEED gasps]
[yelps]
We're supposed to be invincible!
Two of them are behind us!
[SPEED]
That rock!
I'll split it!
[screams]
You got both of them!
Now hurry up!
You've got to stop the others!
[gasps]
[screams]
[SPEED]
No place to hide!
With that monster
submarine up there,
we won't hafta worry
about the kid.
[ASSASSIN H] He's been able to
avoid the fire missiles so far,
but he can't keep it up.
I'm gonna finish him off now.
[ASSASSIN H]
Oh... Missed again!
But I'll smash him this time!
I've got him in perfect range.
These shots'll do it.
Here goes!
[BOTH yell]
That was a direct hit!
Come on, we've gotta jump out!
They're like sitting ducks.
I'll just finish 'em off.
[groans]
He was a sitting duck.
Now there's no one
at the controls.
We'd better get out of here
while we still can, Chim Chim.
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
Look, the monster
submarine's going to crash!
Get down, Trixie!
Speed, we finished the job!
We're coming down!
Look out below!
That's Spritle up there.
He was in the submarine!
It's headed straight
for the assassins.
A bullseye!
That takes care of
those awful men!
[SPRITLE]
Racer X!
[SPEED]
[TRIXIE]
Racer X!
[SPRITLE] We took care of
all the assassins.
A fine job.
[DIPLOMAT F]
The entire world
will be grateful
for what you've done.
[SPEED]
Racer X, I've been wondering...
Are you some
kind of secret agent?
[RACER X chuckles]
No, Speed.
I'm a professional
racing driver...
...and your closest competitor.
I'll always be.
[SPEED]
And I'm your closest competitor.
I'll always be!
[NARRATOR] The assassin gang
has been defeated.
But more thrills,
more races, more adventures
are on the road ahead in the
next thrilling episode of...
...Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪