♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[SPRITLE]
Pops built a fabulous mini-racer
as a gift for Prince Jam,
who lived in this palace
in the country of Saccarin.
I wanted to meet Prince Jam
and watch the Baby Grand Prix,
but Pops told me
there was no room
for Chim Chim and
me on the trip.
I was disappointed,
but I figured out a plan.
And when that plane took off
for Saccarin, I was on it!
[SPRITLE chuckles] Pops didn't
know that I was hidden
in the car inside a suitcase.
But Speed found me,
and chased Chim Chim and me
into an oriental temple!
In that same temple,
three mysterious men
were chasing Prince Jam.
The Prince and I
crashed into each other,
and the soldiers got mixed up
and thought I was Prince Jam!
They took me to the palace.
But I didn't mind, because I was
able to race in the Grand Prix
because everyone thought
I was the Prince.
It was fun making believe
I was Prince Jam.
[SPRITLE]
Everything was going okay
until those three mysterious
men joined the race.
You're in for it, Prince!
We fixed the car up!
[screams]
[SPRITLE]
I had to stop and find out
what they had done to the car.
[groans]
[tires screech]
[SPRITLE] I stopped,
but it was in the middle
of that dangerous bridge!
[gasps]
Help me!
[SPRITLE]
Speed was on the way.
[SPEED gasps]
[screams]
[CHIM CHIM screams]
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[GUARDS] Prince Jam!
Prince Jam! Prince Jam!
[KING whimpers]
If I had known this was going
to happen to Prince Jam,
I would never have let
him join the Grand Prix.
You're wrong to blame the race
for Prince Jam's disaster.
The Grand Prix has nothing to
do with what happened to him!
Oh?
What do you blame for
what happened to him?
Your Majesty, I
blame Pops Racer.
He built the Prince's car,
and so he is the one to blame!
It shouldn't have crashed!
[KING sighs]
I'm afraid you're
right, Offendem.
There's only one thing left
for you to do, Your Majesty.
You must have Pops Racer
and the members
of the Mach 5 team
punished for the crime!
Huh?
[OFFENDEM] I've ordered the
soldiers to bring them here.
They must be punished.
Oh, and, by the way...
Although I realize how badly
you feel about Prince Jam,
I must talk to you about
a very serious matter
concerning our
country's welfare.
I feel too sad about
Prince Jam to discuss anything.
[OFFENDEM]
But Your Majesty--
Please, leave me alone
for a while, Offendem!
I just don't feel like
talking right now.
But you must, Your Majesty!
After all, the
coronation ceremony
is scheduled to take
place very shortly!
And with Prince Jam gone,
you've got to decide
who will succeed you!
Right now I don't care who
will succeed me on the throne!
[OFFENDEM] Mm... Then it'll
be Prince Sugarin
who will take over
the throne from you.
Do you agree, Your Highness?
[KING] I don't have
any other choice, do I?
[OFFENDEM chuckles]
That's right!
Why are you so happy about it?
It'll be terrible!
[OFFENDEM] Oh, I agree,
Prince Sugarin won't be as good
a ruler as Prince Jam
would have been,
but leave all the
arrangements to me,
and I'll make sure
the country is run
the way we want it to be run.
[KING groans]
Very well...
[GUARD A]
We've arrested Pops Racer
and one of the Mach 5 team.
We blame you completely for
Prince Jam's disaster
in the Grand Prix!
And so, you and the
others on your team
will be punished
for building a car
which has caused us
to lose Prince Jam,
the beloved successor
to his father's throne!
You can't blame us!
That was a perfect car!
Keep quiet!
That car would not have crashed
if it had been perfect!
That's your opinion!
I designed and built that car
so it wouldn't cause
any trouble at all!
If that's so, then how come
it crashed the way it did?!
I don't know why it crashed!
Lock them both up and
throw away the key!
[GUARD A]
Move!
[OFFENDEM]
Wait!
Why hasn't Speed Racer
been arrested?
He was chasing
Prince Jam in the Mach 5,
and we weren't able
to catch up to him.
If Speed ever gets back,
we'll learn what really
happened to Prince Jam.
[OFFENDEM]
Silence!
Find Speed Racer, and when
you do, throw him in jail!
He's as guilty as the
rest of those criminals!
[GUARD A]
Yes, sir.
[OFFENDEM] I've got to get
Speed out of the way
before he discovers my scheme.
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[SPRITLE gasps]
Where am I?!
Oh...! Now I remember!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[SPRITLE]
Speed! He's been hurt!
[car honks]
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[SPEED groans]
Speed! Speed! Speed, wake up!
[SPEED gasps]
Your Majesty, Prince Jam!
[SPRITLE] No, Speed. Can't you
tell? I'm not the Prince!
I may look like that Prince,
but it's me, Spritle.
[SPEED]
Huh?
Well, I must admit you
sound like my brother, sir.
That's funny, Speed.
You called me "sir."
Maybe you are Spritle,
'cause there's Chim Chim.
That's right!
Then how come you were posing
as Prince Jam in the race?
I don't really know how
it happened to me, Speed,
but everybody thought
I was Prince Jam.
Everybody thought it?!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
Then the real Prince
is back in the hotel!
Let me out! Let me out!
We locked him up!
We thought it was you! Come on!
[NARRATOR] But the real
Prince managed to escape.
[SHOP KEEPER]
No money, no food! Get out!
You can't do this to me!
Who do you think I am?!
I'm Prince Jam of Saccarin!
And when I demand
food, I get it.
And I'm hungry, so I
demand food right now!
Give it to me!
--[CHILDREN laughing]
--[PRINCE JAM] Huh?
[PRINCE JAM]
Hm! That food looks delicious;
I command you to give me some!
[CHILDREN laughing]
[GUARDS laughing]
So, you claim you're the Prince,
eh? The Prince of what?
The Kingdom of Dirt and Grime?
[GUARDS laughing]
You'll be sent to jail!
[GUARDS]
Huh?!
Sent to jail, eh?
[PRINCE JAM grunting]
Let go!
[GUARD B]
Jail, eh?
[screaming]
[WOMEN laughing]
[PRINCE JAM screaming]
[PEOPLE laughing]
I'm the Prince!
Why doesn't anyone believe
that I'm Prince Jam?
Everybody's being so mean
to me; I don't know why.
They shouldn't judge somebody
by the clothes he's got on.
[screams]
[PRINCE JAM]
Help!
[PRINCE JAM panting]
--[TRENCHCOAT MAN laughs]
--[PRINCE JAM gasps]
[TRENCHCOAT MAN]
Hello, Highness.
Who are you? Huh?!
[TRENCHCOAT MAN] You are
the real Prince, I presume?
Of course! Can't you tell?
[TRENCHCOAT MAN laughs]
You look as if you've been
starving, Your Highness.
Wouldn't you like some food?
You mean, you really believe
that I'm Prince Jam?
[TRENCHCOAT MAN]
Not quite.
But I will if you show me
the royal birthmark!
Fair enough.
This proves beyond any
doubt that I'm Prince Jam.
[TRENCHCOAT MAN]
So it does.
[PRINCE JAM gasps]
And I know who you are!
[screams]
[VILLAIN A]
After him!
[PRINCE JAM]
Help!
[VILLAIN A]
Get him!
[VILLAIN B]
Gotcha!
[PRINCE JAM screams]
[VILLAIN C]
Gotcha!
[PRINCE JAM gasps]
[VILLAIN A]
Gotcha!
[PRINCE JAM screaming]
[VILLAIN C] How come you're
alive, Prince Jam?
[VILLAIN B] We thought you
fell into that gorge
when the bridge collapsed.
[VILLAIN C]
We can't let you get in the way
of Prince Sugarin
taking over the throne.
[VILLAIN B]
We thought you were an imposter;
now you'll wish you were!
[VILLAIN A]
Enough! Let's get it over with!
[VILLAIN B]
Right.
[VILLAIN C]
Wait a minute!
We'd better tell Offendem
before we finish the job.
[VILLAIN B]
But if we tell him,
he'll find out the
Prince is still alive,
and he thinks we finished
him off long ago.
Let's finish him now!
[VILLAIN A] But if we
capture the Prince alive,
he'll be worth so
much more money!
Capture him!
[PRINCE JAM gasps]
[NARRATOR]
Speed hurries to the hotel
in which he and Pops had
held the real Prince Jam,
thinking he was Spritle.
[SPEED]
He's gone!
And it looks as if there
was a flood in here!
[MANAGER]
There was!
Huh?
It was caused by that little boy
you had locked up in here
turning the water
spigots on full force.
When this door was opened,
there was such a flood,
it's a wonder the entire
hotel wasn't washed away.
I'm very sorry.
But the way, this
gentleman's from the palace,
and wants to ask some questions.
[TRENCHCOAT MAN]
What happened to the Prince?
All I know is that
some mysterious men
were chasing Prince Jam.
They tried to get
rid of him when
they thought he was
racing in the Grand Prix.
[TRENCHCOAT MAN]
How do you know all that?
My brother, Spritle,
told me. He saw them.
[TRENCHCOAT MAN]
Your brother?
[SPEED] I think they're trying
to get rid of Prince Jam
so they can put someone
else on the throne.
You've gotta find
the real Prince Jam
before something
terrible happens to him.
[TRENCHCOAT MAN]
You and your brother seem to
know the whole scheme.
Where is Spritle right now?
I told him to wait
outside in the Mach 5.
[TRENCHCOAT MAN]
Is that so?
Well, Speed, it's too bad,
but you and your
brother know too much!
--[VILLAINS grunt, yelp]
--[SPEED grunts]
Spritle, be careful!
[SPRITLE]
Help!
[SPEED groans]
[VILLAIN A]
We'll carry him out.
[VILLAIN B]
Ow!
[gasps]
[DRIVERS grunting]
Get him, boys!
After them!
[VILLAIN A]
Ready?
[VILLAIN C]
Yeah.
[VILLAIN A]
Let's go!
[VILLAIN B] I've got to get
that kid. He knows too much!
[VILLAIN B groans]
[CHIM CHIM laughs]
[SPRITLE] Just then, I bumped
into the real Prince Jam.
So you see, I'm
really Spritle Racer.
I'm not even related
to the Prince!
But the Prince is being held
prisoner somewhere, I think.
The whole dirty scheme started
when one of the King's ministers
by the name of Offendem planned
to get rid of Prince Jam
and put Prince Sugarin
on the throne instead.
He hired this character
and two of his partners
to do all the dirty work.
Isn't that right?!
I-I won't say a word.
Chim Chim, make him talk.
--[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
--Stop that! Cut it out, Monkey!
Look! Only ten more minutes
before the coronation!
Tell us, where's
the real Prince Jam?
Don't ask me.
[gibbers]
All right! I'll talk! Only,
don't let that monkey hurt me!
The Prince is being held
in Punchkey Temple.
But by the time you rescue
him, it'll be too late.
And our Prince Sugarin
will be on the throne.
And then we'll have every one
of you locked up forever!
What'll we do? Huh?
Tell the police at the palace.
[VILLAIN B] That won't work
because Minister Offendem's men
already control parts
of the palace.
We'll use an imposter and we'll
take the imposter to the palace.
An imposter?
[DRIVER A] Right, and you
look like the Prince,
so you'll be the imposter.
Again?
Why not?
We'll break up into two groups.
One will take you to the palace,
and the other will take
him to Punchkey Temple
to get the real Prince Jam
out of the jam he's in.
Good plan. Let's hurry.
[trumpets playing]
[NARRATOR]
The ceremony begins--
The coronation to crown Prince
Sugarin instead of Prince Jam.
[GUARD C]
Halt!
[DRIVER A] Clear the way!
Prince Jam is here!
[GUARDS gasp]
[KING]
Do you swear, Prince Sugarin,
to keep the country of Saccarin
in peace for all time?
Yup.
[OFFENDEM chuckles]
[DRIVER B]
Stop!
[OFFENDEM]
Huh? Prince Jam is alive!
[KING]
Huh? Alive?! My son?
M-My son! My son is alive!
--[SPRITLE] Daddy, Your Majesty!
--[PEOPLE chattering]
[DRIVERS]
Long live Prince Jam!
May he live forever!
Then we can't blame your absence
on a faulty mini-racing
car, can we, son?
No, Daddy. That man
there's to blame,
your minister, Offendem.
[PEOPLE murmuring]
Don't worry, I'll make sure that
Offendem pays for his crime.
I'll put him on trial later,
but in the meantime,
we must release Pops Racer and
Trixie from jail immediately.
Bring them here!
Prince Jam, thank you for
all you've done for us.
[SPRITLE]
Ssh, it's me, Pops--Spritle.
[POPS gasps]
[OFFENDEM]
Stoneheads!
Prince Jam ruined the coronation
by showing up alive and well.
You've bungled another job.
[VILLAIN C]
But that's impossible.
[VILLAIN A]
Yeah, or rather, an imposter!
Prince Jam is a prisoner
right here with us.
We're gonna take care of him
along with our other
prisoner, Speed Racer.
Maybe that imposter who looks
so much like the Prince
is Speed's kid brother, Spritle.
That would figure,
because my partner,
who was chasing Spritle,
hasn't reported in yet!
[OFFENDEM]
Mm...
An imposter!
Do you solemnly
swear, Prince Jam,
to keep the country of Saccarin
in peace for all time?
You bet!
[OFFENDEM]
Wait, he's a fake!
Uh-oh!
That Prince is an imposter!
You mean, he's not my son?!
[OFFENDEM] The real Prince Jam
has the birthmark of a clover
on his left arm. See if
that imposter has it.
Oh!
Now you're going to be
in plenty of trouble.
[VILLAIN A] Now I'll finish
you two off for good!
[BOTH gasp]
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[PRINCE JAM screams]
[VILLAIN A]
Wait a minute!
Ah-hah!
--[SPEED] Come on!
--[VILLAIN C groans]
[VILLAIN A]
Stop him!
--[DRIVER C] Speed!
--[SPEED gasps]
[DRIVERS] Hurry! Come on!
Jump down! Hurry up!
Hang on!
[PRINCE JAM, SPEED grunt]
[SPEED]
Are you all right, Your Majesty?
[PRINCE JAM]
Perfectly. Come on, let's hurry.
It's great. The children
in this country
are trying to help
you, Your Majesty.
[PRINCE JAM]
But why?
[SPEED] Well, I guess they
just don't wanna see you
cheated out of the throne,
which is rightfully yours.
[VILLAIN A]
Call Offendem.
And tell him he better stop them
or else he'll never get
Prince Sugarin crowned.
Well, he has no birthmark
on his left arm,
and that proves that
he's an imposter.
What do you want
me to do with him?
[SPRITLE grunts]
Your Royal Majesty Highness,
there's a reason I
pretended to be your son.
You've got to let me explain!
Shut up, brat.
Arrest him and all
those children outside
for disrupting the coronation.
[GUARD D]
Yes, sir.
[gasps]
[GUARDS]
Halt!
[GUARDS gasp]
[PRINCE JAM, SPEED grunt]
[ALL gasp]
Your Majesty, I brought the real
Prince Jam--the future King.
It's true! I can
see his birthmark!
Mm! My son! My son!
[PRINCE JAM]
Daddy!
[KING sobs]
Oh, my son...
[PEOPLE chattering]
[OFFENDEM growls]
[trumpets playing]
[KING] Do you solemnly
swear, real Prince Jam,
to keep the country of Saccarin
in peace for all time?
I do.
[bells chime]
[ALL laugh]
[POPS chuckles]
Well, it looks as if
everyone's finally happy
in the Kingdom of Saccarin.
For a while, it looked bad.
I heard on the radio
that Minister Offendem
has disappeared.
[POPS]
Good!
After what he's done,
I'd be ashamed to
show my face anywhere
if I were him,
which I'm glad I'm not.
He's a menace to racing
drivers and everyone else.
Good riddance!
And this'll be in tip-top
shape for Prince Jam
to drive in the Baby
Grand Prix tomorrow.
If I were just two days older,
I could drive in
the race with him.
[TRIXIE]
You won't be eight years old
till day after tomorrow.
That's true, so forget
about the race.
Wait a minute! You will
be able to race!
Huh?
Please don't tell me
things like that, Speed,
unless you really mean them.
[sighs]
We forgot about
the time difference.
[POPS]
Hm?
Time difference, Speed?
[SPEED]
Right.
According to our time,
Spritle won't be eight
years old for two days.
But we flew halfway around
the world to get here.
And we picked up a day!
The day after tomorrow is really
tomorrow here in Saccarin.
That means Spritle
will be eight tomorrow!
You're absolutely right!
Spritle can race!
[TRIXIE gasps]
[SPRITLE]
Hurray!
--[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
--[SPRITLE chuckles]
It's going to be tough, Speed.
You know why? We've gotta
build another car by tomorrow!
If anybody can build
a car that fast, you can.
And if anybody can win
the race, Spritle can!
[ANNOUNCER]
Prince Jam and Spritle are
fighting it out for first place!
Hey! [chuckles]
[laughs]
[NARRATOR] Spritle and Prince
Jam tie for first place.
There's more excitement
and danger ahead
in the next episode
of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪