♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[SPEED]
This is the second day
of the most dangerous
race in the world.
And this most treacherous
part of the entire course
is so full of landslides
caused by the heavy rain,
that some drivers were
too afraid to go on.
But six of us, Racer X, myself,
and members of the
Car Acrobatic Team
decided to continue,
and we drew lots to see
which of us would go first.
It would be
increasingly hazardous
for each man who followed.
What position'll you be in?
[SPEED]
Last!
I'll be the one to make it.
[SPEED] No one had been
able to cross the chasm,
and now it was
Racer X's turn to try.
[SPEED] It's my turn now,
and I've got to make it.
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, in a nearby lodge,
Sparky, Trixie, and
Spritle watch the storm
and wait anxiously
for news of the race.
According to this bulletin,
not much information is
available because of the storm,
but apparently, more
than a dozen cars,
including members of the Car
Acrobatic Team and the Mach 5,
have had their way blocked
near Yarning Chasm pass.
The racing committee is
considering changing the course
to a less dangerous area
before the cars and drivers
are completely wiped out.
[TRIXIE]
Oh...
I hope Speed'll be all right.
I hope he won't try to go ahead.
I'm not worried.
He took my good luck charm
along in the car with him,
and it'll bring him good
luck, right, Chim Chim?
Won't it, Sparky?
Say he'll be all right!
[SPRITLE wailing]
[ALL gasp]
Aren't you men supposed
to be in the race?
We barely managed to make it
back from Yarning Chasm Pass.
The road's impassible.
Do you know what happened
to some of the other drivers
in the race?
Most of them will
never come back.
[gasps]
They tried to make it from one
cliff to the other and failed.
[groans]
You said they didn't make it?
Their cars were wrecked?
There was nothing left of them
including the cars of
the Car Acrobatic Team.
They were stupid to try to go
ahead when everybody could see
that they wouldn't
be able to make it.
Poor Speed.
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
All right, Sparky, come on.
[SPARKY]
Where?
Speed might need help!
I wanna try to help him!
Hey, you'd better wait
till this storm blows over!
Don't worry; we'll be all right.
But as soon as the
weather's calmed down,
we'll send out a searching
party to look for him.
[TRIXIE] I'm sorry, but by
then, it might be too late.
I'm going now.
[INFORMANT] No, you'll never
get through. You'd better wait.
I've got to try to help Speed
right now! Let go of my arm.
Hey, no matter what you say,
we're gonna try
to help my brother.
Let's go, come on!
The storm's bad. Stay!
I won't let you out there.
[grunting]
[INFORMANT yelps]
Come back here!
[SPRITLE]
Let's go!
You'll be sorry!
Poor Speed...
I hope we find him...
[engine sputters]
[gasps]
There's not a drop of gas
left in the tank! Oh...
[TRIXIE]
Speed! Speed!
Oh, Speed!
[cackles]
[gasps]
I am not Speed as Speed
Racer no longer exists.
[shrieking]
[gasping]
[groaning]
[SPEED]
Oh, my eyes! It hurts my eyes.
[SPEED] What's the matter
with me? I can't see.
It's Spritle's good luck charm!
[SPRITLE]
If you carry it with you,
it'll bring you good
luck and you'll win.
[SPEED] Where's the
Mach 5? I've gotta find it.
Where is it?
[SPEED] I hope the Mach 5
hasn't been damaged.
I'll go on with the race
even though I can't see.
I've got to beat the
Car Acrobatic Team.
[SPEED]
Where is it? Where's the Mach 5?
[thunk]
[SPEED]
Who's there? Huh?
Snake. So you're still
alive, huh, Speed?
I'm surprised that
after that crash you are.
What's your story, Speed?
Don't tell me the Mach 5
isn't running anymore.
[SPEED]
Where is the car?
You're unable to see now?
Well, isn't that just too bad.
Snap out of it.
[crying]
It looks as if I'm gonna
win the Alpine Race.
You better wait here till
somebody rescues you.
I'm glad to say your racing
days are over for good, Speed.
Heh.
I guess I proved I'm a much
better driver than you, Speed.
I'm on my way to victory!
[SPEED gasps]
[NARRATOR]
Racer X.
Unknown to Speed, this
is his older brother Rex,
who ran away from
home years ago.
I smell the oil of
the Mach 5's engine.
I started it.
But how am I going to drive
without seeing the road?
I recognize the
sound of that car.
It can only belong to Racer X
and that must mean that
he's come back into the race.
Well, so have I! Here goes!
[gasps]
[RACER X]
Keep at it, Speed.
You've got a chance
to make it...
...if you're lucky.
I'm stuck. The grip tires
seem to be broken.
[RACER X]
Easy, Speed. Ease it out gently.
[RACER X] Come on, Speed.
You can't give up now.
It sounds as if
Racer X is leaving
and he won't give me any help.
I'm on my own.
[RACER X] I can't leave
him there like that,
but what choice do I have?
What can I do?
That was a bad crash.
I hope he hasn't been hurt.
[SPEED]
Racer X!
Where are you?
Racer X! Where are you?
[groans] Over here, Speed...
He sounds badly hurt.
But where is he?
Racer X!
Here! Over here!
[SPEED]
I'm coming.
[RACER X] Speed,
you're a brave, young man.
I'm proud to have
you for a brother.
[SPEED] Where are you,
Racer X? I can't find you.
Racer X, are you hurt badly?
I think my legs have
been broken, Speed.
Well, hang on to me. I'll try
to get you into the Mach 5.
Speed, don't bother about me,
you need help yourself.
Your eyes must hurt you.
Neither one of us will be
able to go on with the race.
Snake Oiler is the only one
of the Car Acrobatic Team
who's continuing in the race.
Snake Oiler, huh?
I wanna beat him more
than anything in the world.
Your car's the
only other one left,
but you can't see and
I can't even walk,
so Snake's liable to win.
But, Speed, I have an
idea that just might work.
Huh?
You be my legs, and at the
same time, I'll be your eyes.
[SPEED]
Oh, I get it!
You and I will be a team.
Yes. Maybe we can overtake
Snake and win. Come on.
[RACER X]
My legs are perfectly all right,
but this is the only way
I can help my brother Speed.
No Mach 5 or Speed.
[SPARKY]
Uh-oh.
Maybe the Mach 5's been
completely wrecked.
I feel that somewhere down
there, Speed's all right.
I think so, too, because he
has my good luck charm.
[SPARKY]
We'll follow the course.
Keep a sharp eye out for him.
There's the Mach 5!
[SPRITLE, SPARKY]
And there's Speed!
Left. Now ten degrees right.
Get ready, here comes
another turn to the right.
Fifteen degrees to the right.
[TRIXIE]
Speed. Speed!
Go ahead, Trixie.
[TRIXIE]
Are you all right, Speed?
[SPEED]
I... It's my eyes.
[TRIXIE] What's the
matter with your eyes?!
Uh, I'm perfectly all
right, don't worry.
Nothing's wrong with them.
[TRIXIE] I think you're
fibbing to me, Speed.
Make a left.
Who's that riding
with you, Speed?
[SPEED] Racer X. He hurt
his legs in a crash.
Hi, Speed, I'm up here, too!
[SPARKY]
Me, too!
[CHIM CHIM yells]
[SPEED] All of you, huh?
That's just great.
Now all I have to do
is beat Snake Oiler.
I might be able to catch up to
him in the next few minutes.
I'll meet you at the finish
line, Trixie, how 'bout it?
[TRIXIE] I'll be waiting for
you, Speed. Good luck!
Faster!
The final check point
is 250 yards up ahead.
Put your brakes on.
I'm glad to see you
reached here safely.
Now, why don't you
both take a break?
[SPEED]
I don't want one.
But, Speed, you need a rest.
Have you seen the Car
Acrobatic Team's car?
A car passed by this
checkpoint within the hour.
Thanks! Hang on!
Are you all right, Speed?
Yes. I won't rest until
Snake's been beaten.
Well, then, you'll have
to hurry. Give her the gun.
That's it. Give her even more.
Even faster!
I see him! He's just ahead!
At last, Speed,
we've caught up to him.
The Mach 5!
And I thought I was the only
driver left in the race.
You'll never be able to
follow me over this chasm.
Go ahead, Speed. It's your
turn to try to get over that
without crashing down to
those rocks in the bottom!
Speed! There's a broken bridge
up ahead! Use your brakes!
Snake managed to get across
it, didn't he? So will I!
How? That bridge
is falling apart!
Speed, you'd better use the
brakes before it's too late
and we smash up!
Tell me when we get
to the broken bridge.
I'm gonna try to get across it.
The Acrobatic Team's cars have
special equipment for flying.
The Mach 5 can't do it!
Use the brake!
[SPEED]
I'm giving her the gas!
Stop!
Speed, we can't make it!
Jam on the brakes! Quick!
You made it. I don't think
you would've been able to do it
with your eyes open.
There was no other way.
I had to make it.
Now I've gotta win.
[ANNOUNCER]
The Alpine Race is almost over.
And, because of the terrific
storm and the dangerous course,
out of the starting
lineup of 86 cars,
only two cars are
still in the race.
One of them is car number 12,
driven by Snake Oiler
of the Car Acrobatic Team.
And the other is the Mach 5
driven by Speed Racer.
Ladies and gentleman,
if you look to your left,
you can see the
remaining members
of the Car Acrobatic Team
waiting for the end of the race.
[TEAM MEMBER A]
Captain Terror!
[CAPTAIN TERROR]
Yes?
I just got a report that
Snake is way in the lead.
Snake's my brother
and he's going to bring
a glorious victory to
the Car Acrobatic Team.
[CAPTAIN TERROR]
We will be famous
as the greatest racing
team in the world!
No one can beat us!
Hurry, Snake! Bring us
the crown of victory!
It's hard to catch up to him.
He's liable to win.
If only I could see,
I'd go even faster.
But Speed, you mustn't give up.
Why not? I don't think I have
a chance of beating him.
Speed, you still have
a chance to win.
I can see something you can't.
Oil is leaking from Snake's car.
Oil?
If he keeps on going
at his present speed,
he's gonna blow up.
He may notice
the trouble though,
and take time out
to stop the leak.
I don't think he'll
even notice it.
Snake's paying
too much attention
to the road in front of him.
Then he'll be wiped out
if his car blows up.
Yes, it might be the end of him.
But we're not gonna help him,
not if you wanna win the race.
It wouldn't be right.
I've got to try to warn him.
It's only fair.
Okay.
You're doing the right thing,
Speed, in trying to warn him.
Thanks.
Huh?!
The Mach 5 again...
And it's gaining on me.
I can't pull away from it.
Snake, be careful!
There's something wrong
with your engine.
You're leaking oil very badly!
I'm not fallin' for that trick.
I'm not gonna stop.
Snake, I'm not lying!
He won't believe you, and you've
done your best to warn him.
Hang on.
[ANNOUNCER] And now
approaching the finish line
is car number 12
driven by Snake Oiler.
It looks as if he'll
be the winner.
Oh! But here comes the Mach 5
with Speed Racer at the wheel!
Look at them go!
Go, Speed, go!
Go!
C'mon, Speed! You can do it!
I'm gonna win!
I'm gonna beat Speed!
[laughs]
[BOTH gasp]
[screams]
[SPEED]
Snake wouldn't listen...
[ALL shouting]
--[SPARKY] You won, Speed!
--[SPRITLE] You did it!
You drove a magnificent
race, Speed Racer,
and you fully deserve to be
the winner and champion.
Now go to the hospital
where the doctors will
make your eyes well again.
We will never forget this race
and our defeat by the
Mach 5 and Speed Racer.
[groans] We'll get revenge...
[CAPTAIN TERROR]
Snake is right.
There will be other races
and chances for vengeance.
We shall plan for the
day when once again,
we will compete
against Speed Racer,
and on that day,
we shall not fail.
Let's go home.
[RACER X] Speed, you
could be a great driver,
but you can also
be a great man.
You value a life even
higher than victory.
The world needs more
people like you.
I'm proud to have
you as a brother.
Have you seen Racer X? I've
gotta find him to thank him.
I saw him in the Mach 5
only a few minutes ago.
Nobody's in the car now.
There isn't? That means he was
able to walk away from it.
His legs weren't broken.
He just told me that so
I'd let him help me drive.
He deserves this trophy, not me.
Oh, Speed! All that matters to
me is that you made it safely.
Now let's go to the hospital
and get your eyes taken care of.
[NARRATOR]
Speed has just won
the most dangerous
race in the world,
but even more danger
and thrills lie just ahead.
Be sure to ride
with Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪