♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
Ladies and gentlemen, the
fabulous Stunt Car Spectacular
is about to take place.
Get ready for
action and thrills!
There will be rewards
for the most skillful
and daring drivers.
[ANNOUNCER] Anyone who wishes
to compete in tonight's contests
is invited to join the
Stunt Car Spectacular.
[ANNOUNCER] The first
contestant is Mr. Guts Wheeler!
[CROWD gasping]
He wasn't a good driver,
the way he crashed up.
Speed, you can do
better than that.
[ANNOUNCER] Next contestant,
Mr. High Octane.
[groaning]
[BOTH gasp]
[SPRITLE]
Wow!
Oh, look over there! Isn't
that the boy, Speed Racer?
That's him, all right.
Let's ask him for his autograph.
[GIRL A]
Can we have your autograph?
Boy, oh boy, is my
brother Speed popular.
--[GIRL B] He's cute!
--Oh... Thanks... Speedy!
[GIRL C]
Let me shake your hand.
[GIRL C giggles]
[TRIXIE]
Oh.
And you must be Speed Racer.
[SPEED]
Huh?
I was told that you're one
of the greatest racers
in the world, is that true?
Who are you anyway?
Snake Oiler's the name, and
I'm a pretty good racer, myself.
Why don't we have a race to
see which one of us is better?
[SPEED]
Okay, let's go.
[SNAKE]
Make the pile of cars higher.
You'll never be able to make it!
Don't argue with me;
do as I say. Make it higher!
[ANNOUNCER]
Next, Mr. Snake Oiler!
He did it!
Snake Oiler just drove over
the top of the biggest stack
we've had yet!
Mr. Oiler is a star member
of the world famous
Car Acrobatic Team.
[SPEED] He's on the
Car Acrobatic Team, huh?
Well, I've sure heard of them.
All right, ladies and gentlemen!
Who'll now try to beat him?
I was just warming up.
Everybody's gonna have to do
some fancy driving to beat that!
How 'bout you, Speed?
Can you beat me?
I don't know.
[SPRITLE]
Huh?!
What do you mean, Speed?
You can beat him!
Go ahead, try it.
Are you scared?
You better not try it,
Speed, because if you crash,
I'll lose my best competitor
in the next Alpine Race.
[SPRITLE gasps]
[SPEED]
I'll try!
[SPRITLE]
Hurray! Hurray!
I'll get over the top.
Don't, Speed!
You'll never make it!
[SPARKY]
Trixie's right, Speed.
Now, don't do it!
Remember how important
the Big Alpine Race will be.
If something happens to you
now, you'll be out of it!
Just look how high
that stack is!
[SPEED]
She's right, all right.
If I'm going to beat Snake, I'll
beat him in the Alpine Race.
I'll have a better
chance to win that.
Well, I've got to! I've got
to win the Alpine Race!
I know Speed can
drive over that,
but right now, he's nothing
but a scared chicken! Phooey!
He's brave!
It takes real courage to decide
not to challenge Snake here
but to wait for the Alpine Race.
[SPRITLE]
Hmm...
Seems complicated.
[TRIXIE]
You'll understand what I mean
when it's time for that race.
I hope so.
[ALL gasp]
The Car Acrobatic Team!
Daredevil drivers!
[gasps]
[TRIXIE screams]
[CROWD gasps]
[ALL scream]
We'll be seeing you
in the Alpine Race.
[BOTH screaming]
Well, Speed, here
we are in the Alps.
But I don't think you
should enter the big race.
I've got to, Sparky!
I've got to beat the
Car Acrobatic Team.
It'll be too dangerous
even to try!
Why do you say that?
Snake Oiler's one of the
best drivers I've ever seen,
and I figure that some
of the other drivers
on that team are even better!
Sparky, I know they are.
That's why I wanna
try to beat them.
I've got to prove
that I'm the best.
And I'm racing, no
matter what you tell me.
Huh?
But they're tricky, Speed.
They'll use every dirty
trick they know to win.
Do you think I'm afraid? Is
that what you think about me?
If you do, cut it out!
I'm not scared!
[TRIXIE]
Sparky! [gasps]
Sparky was only trying to think
of what might be best for you.
[SPEED]
Hmph.
I'm gonna win.
I'm gonna beat Snake Oiler
and every one of the
Car Acrobatic Team.
[SPEED]
I'm gonna drive even better
than the best racer I've
ever seen, Racer X.
[SPRITLE]
Go, Speed! Go!
[POPS]
A hundred and eighty!
You've done enough practicing
on this special course, Speed.
Now, you practice here
on the first chasm jump
of the Alpine course.
[POPS]
If you don't make the jump,
you'll fall a thousand
feet into the river.
You've got to make it!
[gasps]
The acrobats!
The Car Acrobatic Team!
Well, now I'm gonna try it.
Good luck! Get ready!
Go!
[NARRATOR] Speed does not know
that the driver of this car
is secretly his
older brother Rex,
who ran away from
home years ago.
What's the big idea, Racer X?
I came to warn you;
it's too dangerous.
[gasps]
[RACER X] Be careful of
falling rocks like those.
Last year, they wiped
out a dozen drivers
who could've crossed easily.
[SPEED]
How?
Just by keeping their
minds on their driving
and on the obstacles in the way.
But most drivers are worried
about the cars ahead of them
and how to catch up
and pass them.
So, they sometimes
forget to concentrate
on the course itself.
The plateau areas around
here are very tricky.
The ground is hard.
But when it rains heavily,
the ground loosens and changes.
And tires skid treacherously.
Take my advice, Speed.
Otherwise, this will
be your last race.
Very few cars ever
reach the finish line.
It's just too dangerous.
Then you don't think
I can win, Racer X?
[RACER X] You can only
if you keep your mind
strictly on the hazards
of the course.
Oh, one more thing, Speed.
Listen carefully.
As you race down
toward the big jump,
don't be going too fast.
Because you'll cause
another landslide
and crash down into the river.
Also, when you reach the other
side and start to climb again,
don't try to go straight
up toward the top.
Zigzag along the slope.
It takes longer, but it's safer.
And in the long run,
you'll pick up some time.
Remember, throughout
the whole area,
there are patches of ice.
One wrong twist of
your steering wheel,
and that'll be the end of you.
You'll find this is the toughest
course you've ever raced
and you'll need every ounce
of experience and skill, Speed.
Thanks for the advice.
I'll try to follow
all of it, Racer X.
[chuckles] Because if you
don't run a good race,
I won't enjoy winning.
You'll be in the Alpine Race?!
Speed, I'm going to
win the Alpine Race.
I'm not gonna give you a break.
[chuckles]
I suppose I'll have
to redesign the Mach 5.
Then it'll be a better match
against the Acrobatic Team.
Hmm...
Huh?!
My pipe was here and
now it's disappeared!
[gibbering]
[POPS]
Chim Chim! Put that down!
The Car Acrobatic Team
has some amazing drivers.
They're tricky,
experienced, and fast.
They've got something else, too.
I can't figure out what it is!
[SPEED] If I can find out,
I might be able to beat them.
Right. To win, one should
know the strengths
and weaknesses
of the competition.
Gee, Pops, it won't
be so easy to find out
because that team
comes and goes so fast.
[SPRITLE gasps]
[SPRITLE]
Finding out is a job for us!
[growls]
[SPRITLE screams]
[SPRITLE screaming]
[SPRITLE groans]
[howling]
[SPRITLE gasps]
[ACROBATIC LEADER] Members
of the Car Acrobatic Team!
Tomorrow, the great
Alpine Race begins.
A race which we must not lose!
[ACROBATIC DRIVERS]
We will not lose! We will win!
[ACROBATIC LEADER] Good!
Now, let us gather our strength
from the violence
of the elements!
[ACROBATIC LEADER] I have
decided to enter seven of you
in the Alpine Race.
The fastest,
trickiest, strongest,
and most ruthless seven.
Cobra will read off the names.
[COBRA]
Tiger! Knuckles!
Brawn!
Ugly!
Poison!
Ender!
Snake!
[growls]
You must observe
Captain Terror's
first and most
important racing rule:
Do everything to win.
Stop at nothing.
And if you have to
break the law, break it.
[gasps]
[SPRITLE]
And there's my best shot.
You can see the whole
bottom of the car!
Chim Chim and I did
a great job at spying.
The cars don't seem to have
anything unusual on them.
But every one of
them does, Trixie.
You couldn't spot it because
you're not an expert,
but each one of them
has a special device
to help them jump.
You can see it's
located right here.
This particular part
acts like a wing
when the car is in the air.
[SPEED] They must have a
clever designer, eh, Pops?
The most clever man in
the entire racing world.
[SPRITLE] Then the Mach 5
has no chance of winning.
[POPS]
Well, I'm afraid the other cars
are much better than the Mach 5.
[SPRITLE] Oh, please,
you've gotta do something!
Don't worry, Spritle.
I built the Mach 5,
so now I'll rebuild it.
That's what I like
to hear. Get to work!
Speed, don't you forget.
Driver and car have to
be equally good to win,
so do your best job.
I'll do the best job
of driving I can.
[SPRITLE] Hurry, Pops!
Start rebuilding the Mach 5!
Even I'm going to help!
Speed, you'd better get some
rest. I'll be able to finish up.
I'm all right, Pops. You'd
better get some rest, yourself.
[POPS]
You have a big race tomorrow
and you've gotta be
in top condition for it.
Now don't argue with me!
When I tell you to do
something, you'd better do it!
[hammering, clanging]
Pops, would you
like some coffee?
Oh!
[gasps]
[TRIXIE]
Speed, come in here quickly!
[gasps]
[SPEED]
Pops!
He has a bad fever!
[SPEED]
Oh, no!
[TRIXIE]
Where are you taking him, Speed?
To the nearest hospital.
--Let me take him--
--[SPEED] No.
[TRIXIE]
You've only got a few more hours
before the race starts.
You've got to finish the Mach 5.
[SPEED]
But Pops is more important.
Pops wants you to be
in the race, Speed.
And if he were able to,
he'd tell you that himself.
Now you get back to
work on the Mach 5
while I take him to
the hospital. Go ahead!
All right.
[SPEED]
I wish Sparky were here to help.
Only half an hour
before the race starts.
In only half an hour, the
Great Alpine Race begins.
It's now 4:30 in the morning,
and as the sun is coming up,
I'm flying above the
Alpine Race course.
As you may know, this
is the most grueling race
in the entire world.
The drivers must race for
three full days and nights,
facing all kinds of dangers.
Already, more than a million
spectators have gathered
to witness this
spectacular car classic.
And we can promise them,
and you people watching at home
over your television sets,
more thrills, more chills
than you've ever seen before.
There are 86 cars entered.
And most of them are getting
last-minute adjustments
before the start.
Here comes the
Car Acrobatic Team.
Seven of the fastest
and trickiest drivers
anyone has ever seen anywhere.
[ANNOUNCER] Driving car number
9, the mysterious Racer X.
Nobody knows who he is
or where he came from.
Twenty more minutes
before the start.
[ANNOUNCER] All entries,
take starting positions!
[ANNOUNCER]
The race starts in 15 minutes!
[SPEED]
Now I'll see if the wings work.
They do! I've got a chance!
I figured Speed Racer would
be too yellow to turn up,
and I was right; he didn't.
[SPEED] I've got only
three more minutes.
[ANNOUNCER]
Here comes a last-minute entry.
It's the Mach 5,
driven by Speed Racer!
The race starts in 15 seconds!
Try to win, Speed.
But most of all, be careful!
[gasps]
[SPEED] The brakes don't
seem to work very well.
But I checked
everything carefully.
[NARRATOR] The dangerous
Alpine Race is well underway,
and already, there have
been several bad crashes.
Does Speed have a chance to win
against the treacherous
Car Acrobatic Team?
And will Pops be all right?
There are thrills and
terrible dangers ahead.
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪