♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[SPEED] The story begins
on that hot, dusty day
when I was competing in the
first stage of the Sahara Race.
[gasps]
[panting]
[MAN screams]
[tires screech]
[screams]
[SPEED] Are you all right?
Have you been hurt?
Let's go; you'd
better come with me.
Thank you... for your help.
But I'm afraid you're too late.
Huh?
Who are you, sir?
[MAN]
Dr. Digger O. Bone.
I'm an archaeologist.
I came to this country
to see my daughter, Calcia.
But I've had nothing but
misfortune and trouble
since I started out to find her.
For a great many years,
I've been studying about
the ancient Egyptian ruins.
Then, last spring, my
daughter Calcia came here
with my assistant, Splint Femur.
They came to investigate
some of the ancient ruins
and sent me this snapshot,
saying they had
found Cleopatra's tomb.
Do one thing for me--
Try to find them.
I beg you. I-It's
my last request.
Find them.
[DR. BONE groans]
[SPEED]
Doctor! Dr. Bone!
[gasps]
[TRIXIE singing, humming]
[TRIXIE gasps]
I found what those letters mean
that Dr. Bone
scribbled in the sand!
[SPEED]
Huh?
The first letter, "S," stands
for the runes of Sacara.
They're located on
a bank of the Nile.
[SPEED] And the "T" means
the ruins of Taymalamal!
That's it, Trixie!
And the other "T" must stand
for the tomb of Tutankhamen.
You've discovered the key to
what Dr. Bone was
trying to tell me--
The direction and the location
of the tomb of
Cleopatra herself!
Tonight, I'd better go out
and do some investigating.
[TRIXIE]
Tonight, Speed?!
But you're going to miss
the second stage of the race,
and just because you wanna
go looking at old ruins.
Dr. Bone's story
about his daughter
doesn't really concern you.
I'll try to win the
next race, Trixie.
But right now,
I've got something
even more important to do.
Even though I couldn't help
Dr. Bone when he was alive,
maybe I can still help him.
I figure the doctor
must have learned
some very important secret,
and that's why whoever was
in that plane attacked him.
Did ya hear what
he said, Chim Chim?
[SPEED]
See ya later.
[TRIXIE]
Wait!
I wanna go with you, Speed!
[SPEED]
Okay.
By following this route
up along the Nile,
we'll come to the
imperial mausoleums.
And, in that area, should be
what we're looking for.
It's really deserted.
[SPEED]
Mm-hm.
[THUG A]
Too late!
It's getting chilly, Speed.
I'll close the cockpit.
[BOTH gasp]
Whoever they are, they've
made their first move.
[THUG A]
I've failed.
The Mach 5 is proceeding
through the imperial mausoleums.
--[TRIXIE] Oh!
--It's fabulous! Fabulous!
[TRIXIE gasps]
[SPEED]
Those ruins aren't on any map.
Oh, can't you just imagine what
that must've looked
like 3,000 years ago?
[TRIXIE] Do you think
Dr. Bone's daughter, Calcia,
is around here?
[SPEED] She could be, Trixie.
Let's look inside.
I don't see anybody around...
But I have a feeling
we're being watched.
This isn't the older
imperial dynasty construction.
This shows the influence
of the Ptolemaic Dynasty,
and it might've been built
around Cleopatra's time.
I feel as if we're
living 2,000 years ago.
[SPEED]
This pendant!
It's the same one Calcia's
wearing in this picture.
That means she
must've been here!
Oh! And look! Somebody's been
digging in here, recently.
Whoever was in here left behind
some pretty new equipment.
[TRIXIE yelps]
[SPEED]
What's the matter, Trixie?
[TRIXIE]
Look!
[SPEED]
A cobra!
[TRIXIE gasps]
[SPEED]
Don't worry.
Snakes usually just try
to defend themselves.
So as long as we
don't get any closer,
it won't attack us.
That's the largest
cobra I've ever seen!
I wonder if it could
be guarding this place
the way its ancestors
might have done.
[footsteps]
Do you hear that?
I think someone's coming.
[TRIXIE gasps]
[SPEED]
Trixie! Come on!
[SPEED grunts]
[THUG B groans]
[BOTH grunting]
[THUG B screams]
[THUG A groans]
[TRIXIE gasps]
Speed, watch out!
[THUG A groans]
Wait a minute! Come back here!
[SPEED groans]
[THUG A grunting]
[THUG A screams]
[THUG A chuckles]
[gasps]
[THUG A chuckling]
[THUG A]
Now I'll get you!
--[BOTH gasp]
--[TRIXIE screams]
[SPEED screams]
[SPEED grunting]
[TRIXIE]
Speed!
Speed, are you hurt?
My feet are caught!
[TRIXIE]
Oh, I'm coming, Speed!
[SPEED]
No! No, Trixie! Stay away!
[TRIXIE]
I'll help you!
The cobra's right near me;
you've gotta stay away!
[TRIXIE screams]
[cobra croaks]
[SPEED grunts]
--[gasps]
--[SPEED grunting]
[SPEED grunts]
[SPEED]
Trixie, thank you.
[TRIXIE]
Are you all right?
[SPEED]
Uh-huh.
[BOTH gasp]
[CLOAKED MAN chuckles]
Who are you? And what's
the meaning of this?
I know who you are!
You're Dr. Bone's
daughter, Calcia!
I'd know you anywhere.
[CLOAKED MAN] Silence! You're in
the presence of the Queen!
The Queen?!
Let me go!
You are wrong.
I am Cleopatra,
the Queen of the Nile.
[SPEED grunts]
[CALCIA]
I shall not forgive you for
entering my sacred palace
without my permission.
Lock them up!
[CLOAKED MAN]
Yes, Your Majesty.
Take them away!
[CLOAKED MAN, CALCIA laugh]
[TRIXIE]
I don't get it!
[SPEED] I'm sure that
she's really Calcia,
Dr. Bone's daughter.
But why is she pretending
to be Cleopatra?
Something must've
happened to her.
You may be right
about that, Trixie.
Remember where I found
that pendant of hers?
[TRIXIE]
Mm-hm.
There were a lot of fallen
stones lying nearby;
I noticed them!
[SPEED]
That's right.
And Calcia might have been
hit with one of them
when it fell.
It could have affected her mind!
But what happened
to Splint Femur,
her father's assistant?
We haven't seen him yet.
[SPEED]
Hm. I'll bet he'd be able
to solve this whole mystery.
We've gotta try to find him.
Maybe he can help us.
[CLOAKED MAN chuckles]
[SPEED, TRIXIE gasp]
[BOTH]
It's Splint Femur!
All you had to do was
remain in the Sahara Race.
But instead, you tried to
learn too much about me.
Now, you're in my trap.
Your trap?!
[FEMUR]
Without trouble from anyone,
I discovered this place
and found the
treasures of Cleopatra.
But you came along!
And so, now, I must
get rid of you in here,
where the police
will never find you.
You're working with Calcia!
That's right.
We came here together.
And we discovered the
tomb of Cleopatra together.
But then, just as you guessed,
a stone from the roof feel
and struck Calcia on the head.
And, from that moment,
she's been affected.
Calcia thinks she's Cleopatra,
the Empress of the Nile.
I intend to go on
letting her think that.
I won't tell her the truth.
You can't let her
keep on living a lie!
You've got to let her go
back to her own country
for some kind of treatment!
[TRIXIE]
Speed's right!
We're not thinking of
ourselves now, only of her.
Silence!
We haven't dug up
Cleopatra's treasure yet.
And, unless I have
her here as Cleopatra,
those slaves won't cooperate
and help me dig up the treasure.
[SPEED]
Wait, Femur!
Be quiet! Very soon,
you'll be quiet permanently
when I have you put
out of the way for good!
Femur, bring out one
of the prisoners!
[trumpets play]
Hear ye! Speed Racer,
you've been sentenced to fight
against the best
swordsman in the country.
You must fight
against Tetconkin
as your penalty for entering
Her Majesty's palace illegally.
If you win,
you'll be released.
Commence the fight!
[TETCONKIN grunts]
Come up here, but first,
pick up your weapon.
[BOTH grunt]
[TETCONKIN]
I will make you into mincemeat!
[SPEED]
Oh yeah?
[lion growls]
[BOTH grunting]
[lions growling]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[BOTH grunting]
My sword doesn't work like that!
[TETCONKIN chuckles]
[SPEED grunts]
He's not fighting fairly.
[lions growling]
[TETCONKIN grunting]
[SPEED gasping]
[screams]
[TETCONKIN chuckles]
[lions growling]
[SPEED gasping]
[TETCONKIN grunts]
[SPEED groans]
[CROWD gasps]
[lions growling]
[BOTH grunt]
[CROWD gasps]
[gasps]
[TETCONKIN]
Mercy!
You are an amazing and
wonderful young man.
And therefore, I hereby
bestow on you th--
[FEMUR]
Wait!
I must speak to Your Majesty.
[whispers]
All right.
Her Majesty decided to
put you to one more test.
One more?
[FEMUR]
Yes.
On a pyramid like this,
there is a statue of Isis.
The pyramid is 100
miles north of here.
You must go and get the statue
before a shadow reaches
this statue's eyes.
A hundred miles each way,
and you must be back here
within two hours.
That means you must travel
200 miles in only two hours
if you are to succeed.
Two hours--that is all
the time you'll get.
Two hours and that's all.
And if you fail, she
will pay with her life.
You'll never see her again!
[gasps]
[SPEED] Two hundred miles
within only two hours?
I might be able to
make it in the Mach 5.
[SPEED] Calcia--oh,
I mean, Your Majesty.
Will you grant me
just one favor?
[CALCIA]
What?
Will you let me use the Mach 5?
It's the steel chariot which
carried us here to your palace.
[FEMUR]
No. You can't use it.
That wouldn't be fair.
You must go without the car.
[CALCIA]
Be quiet, Femur!
A chariot made of steel
sounds very interesting.
Therefore, you may
use it, young man.
I'll make sure
it won't help him.
He'll never get
back here in time.
[gasps]
[CALCIA]
He has only one more hour left.
I wonder if he has reached
the statue of Isis yet.
[FEMUR]
I wouldn't know, Your Highness.
[gasps]
[SPEED]
Uh-oh!
[THUG C laughs]
That takes care of him!
[SPEED]
You're wrong.
[THUG C yelps]
[THUGS groan]
[SPEED sighs]
The shadow's almost
up to the statue's eyes.
Speed won't make it.
Speed...
Calling headquarters.
Speed is still on his way.
We failed to halt him.
[SPEED]
There it is!
That's the pyramid of
King Tut-Tut on the right.
I've gotta bring back the statue
of Isis if I'm to save Trixie.
But I have less than
an hour to do it in!
He won't make it back
in time, Your Majesty.
Then do what you must.
Bring your torches over to
the stake and light the fire!
[THUGS]
Yes, sir!
[SPEED] I've got to bring
that statue all the way back!
Oh, Speed, forget about me
and don't come back here!
Save yourself!
[SPEED gasps]
[NARRATOR] Will Speed be able
to return the statue
in time to save Trixie?
Or will this attack succeed?
Be sure to see the next
thrilling episode
of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪