♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[NARRATOR]
The hour is midnight.
In a lonely section of town.
[engine revs]
[NARRATOR] The following day,
Speed and Pops are testing
the Mach 5 for a new race.
Fantastic! Two minutes
and six seconds!
That's the third fastest speed
on record for that time.
[SPARKY]
Right!
That's not fast enough!
Speed, you're going to have to
shave it by half a second.
But we were pushing the limit.
It won't do any more than that!
Listen, Speed, it may
not be just the car.
It might be the way
you're driving it.
And maybe it's not my driving.
Maybe you should have built a
little more power into the car.
Hm...
[SPEED] Uh-huh. Well, right now
I'm gonna take a break.
I'm starving.
Huh?!
[gasps]
[TRIXIE]
Uh-oh!
Spritle's been at it again!
Mm!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
Chim Chim, that's mine!
[SPRITLE]
Chim Chim, where are you?
Chim Chim!
Hey! Chim Chim! Chim Chim!
Where are you hiding?
[SPRITLE]
Chim Chim!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
I wonder where he is? He
usually goes only where I go.
[gibbering]
[gasps, grunts]
[shouting]
[chuckles]
[truck rumbles]
[whimpers, gasps]
[growls]
Is that the little chimpanzee
that's so fond of hot dogs?
[GOON 1]
Yeah, that's him, Oriana.
Are you certain that no one
was following the truck?
[GOON 1]
Positive.
[ORIANA] Good. Then get that
chimp ready for the test.
[SPRITLE] I'll try to
help Chim Chim later.
[engine sputters]
[engine revs]
[CHIM CHIM gibbering]
I think you better take
your foot off the gas pedal.
[gibbering continues]
Now give him a squirt.
[shouts]
We'll begin the test.
Wait. Just be patient. Tomorrow
we shall see the results.
--[growling]
--[engine revving]
Chim Chim is really moving! Wow!
We are going to win the
Grand Prix of the Orient!
Mm-hm. We are.
--[CHIM CHIM cheers]
--[SPRITLE] Shh!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
[DOG growls]
[gasps]
[CHIM CHIM]
Uh-oh!
[SPRITLE]
He's out cold! Now's our chance!
[CHIM CHIM laughs]
[SPEED] The car seems
to be in top shape, Pops,
except for a few minor things.
You've got only
three days before
the Oriental Grand Prix, Speed,
and you've gotta pick up
half a second before then.
The acceleration's a bit slow
when I press down on the pedal.
[engine revs]
[SPEED]
See what I mean?
There's nothing wrong
with those RPMs.
That's the way the engine's
supposed to respond.
--[gasps]
--[SPEED] Huh?!
Huh?!
[SPEED] That must be some
kind of new model!
[engine revving]
[POPS]
That sounds familiar!
I've heard that number before!
Somewhere... If only
I could remember!
I don't need any of the formula!
[GOON 1] You won't be able to
handle the GRX without it.
So you get it. Whether
you want it or not!
[coughing]
[POPS] Where have I heard
that engine before?
[tires squeal]
That motor sounds
very familiar. Hmm.
Right! That's the way I feel.
And by the way, you
look familiar to me!
Haven't we met?
No, sir, I'm afraid not.
I've never seen you
before in my life.
[GOON 1]
Eye's ready.
Start!
I've got it! I recognized
the sound of that motor!
It's the GRX!
Huh?! That's 15 seconds
faster than the Mach 5!
[SPEED]
Huh?!
[SPEED] How am I gonna
beat a car that fast?
I wonder who's behind
the wheel of that car?
Let's find out!
[SPARKY]
Okay!
[TRIXIE]
I'm coming, too!
Keep away! You might
run into trouble!
There' something supernatural
about that car!
It might even be a ghost!
I've heard of people ghosts,
so it's perfectly sensible
that there might be
ghosts of certain cars!
You sound as if you know
something about that car!
[POPS]
Hm? Well, I don't.
But take my advice
and don't look at it,
or touch it, or even go
near that strange car!
Who knows what may happen to you
if you meddle in
the supernatural.
And that car's supernatural!
Huh?
Wow! That's sure some car!
I know him!
[POPS]
You know 'im?
Yup!
[POPS]
You're sure, huh?
He gave Chim Chim and me
a terrible time. Awful!
[CHIM CHIM]
Mm-hm!
[POPS]
Hmm...
All right, C'mon, Spritle!
[SPRITLE gasps] Put me down,
Pops! You squeeze too hard!
To the spook cemetery.
[CABBIE]
Yes, sir.
Are we really going
to such a place?
That's where we're
going, Spritle.
[SPRITLE] I don't feel like it.
I wish I'd stayed home.
Do we have to go there?
Yes. I'm going to
look for something
that's supposed to
be buried there.
[SPRITLE whimpers]
Buried there?!
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[OWL hoots]
[BOTH yell]
[yells]
[BATS screech]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH yell]
[TREES giggle]
[yelling]
[POPS]
Hey!
Don't be such a coward!
The both of you get
down and follow me!
Pops! It's pretty late.
Can we go home now?
[POPS grunts]
It's gotta be a ghost!
That must not be real!
[POPS]
It's gone!
Somebody dug it up.
It used to be buried
right down there.
Pops, can't we go home?
[POPS]
Let's go.
There! That's the
place we escaped from.
[POPS] That's Oriana Flub's
house and its secret laboratory.
You stay out here.
[ORIANA]
We have nothing to hide,
so I will be honest
with you, Mr. Racer.
That special car
was built by us.
[POPS coughs]
[ORIANA]
Anything else?
The engine you used is the GRX.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
And whatever engine we built
into the car is our business!
It's my business as well!
You dug that engine
out of the ground!
Out of the tomb of Ben Cranem!
The GRX engine was
built ten years ago.
And five test drivers
crashed because of it.
Even Ben Cranem
himself, the inventor,
crashed because of the GRX!
When we planted Ben Cranem
five years ago
after that terrible crash, we
planted the GRX along with him!
But it was a mistake!
I should have destroyed the
engine with my own hands!
Give me the GRX, now!
It's dangerous!
Let me destroy it the way
I should have years ago!
[ORIANA]
Do you think we are fools?!
Please, give it to me!
--[grunts]
--[POPS groans]
[POPS grunting]
[growls]
[yells]
If you wanna talk with your
muscles, I'm an expert at that!
[GOON 2] Too bad we have
to do this to you.
[grunting]
[gasps]
[POPS]
Huh?
[gasps]
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[grunting]
[growls]
[ORIANA]
Have some sleeper gas!
[groans]
[TRIXIE] Speed. What's the
sense of following that car?
[SPARKY] All Pops said was
that it sounded familiar.
I've gotta find out
more about that car.
Don't try to stop me.
Trixie! Take over the wheel!
[TRIXIE gasps]
I don't know if he
sees what he's doing.
It's pretty dangerous up there.
[LOOMIS] Water! I've
gotta have some water!
[growls]
Slow down! You're
going much too fast!
I can't stand it! Aarg!
Huh? Take it easy.
It won't be much longer.
[yelling]
Pops should've come outta the
house. I wonder what's happened?
[gasps]
Get down!
Ah! That was Speed on the truck!
Now Pops and Speed are
both inside that place.
[machinery whirs]
[GOON 1]
Okay, come on.
[LOOMIS groans]
Are we there, finally?
[GOON 1] Yeah. You can
lie down for a while.
Get some rest.
You'll feel better.
[thudding, grunting]
Go ahead. Report to the police
that we've got that engine.
What good would that do?
Nobody understands how
dangerous that engine can be,
except a professional racer.
The police would do nothing,
so I've got to protect
the racing drivers myself!
[ORIANA] Then you'll risk
even your life to do that?
When I have no choice--
of course I'll risk my life!
[grunts]
[laughs]
You don't believe there's
a racing driver alive
who can safely operate
the GRX, am I right?
At the tremendous speed
that engine can power a car,
nobody has the nerve
or the sharp reflexes
to keep it from crashing.
[ORIANA laughs]
[ORIANA]
You're wrong, Mr. Racer.
There is a driver with
sharp enough reflexes
to drive the car.
And there he is.
[POPS]
Huh?
[DRIVER A groans]
[ORIANA gasps]
[DRIVER A whimpers]
[LOOMIS]
I-I don't wanna drive fast.
I... I-I can't stand
goin' fast. I'm scared.
I don't wanna go fast.
[whimpering continues]
[SPEED] A fantastic looking car.
But what's it's secret?
If I'm gonna try to beat it,
I've gotta learn more about it.
What kind of an
engine does it have?
[gasps]
[SPEED] I've never seen
an engine like this.
[SPEED] I'd give anything
to find out how she handles.
Whoever built this
must be a genius.
[SPEED gasps]
[SPEED]
GRX?
This is that famous engine.
I'm not dreaming. I'm really
looking right at the GRX!
[CURLY]
I suspected that was the GRX.
Huh? You again?
Get away from
that engine, Speed.
I'm going to take it with me.
You have no right!
That's not for you to decide.
Get outta the way.
Neither you, or anybody else is
gonna to stop me from taking it.
[SPEED]
Oh, no?
[SPEED grunts]
[grunting]
Now, go on! Get out of here!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[SPEED grunts]
You won't stop me.
It's gonna be mine, Speed.
[grunting]
Had enough yet, or would you
like to have some more, huh?
[grunts]
You can stay right there
till we figure out how to
get rid of you permanently.
[POPS grunts]
[SPRITLE]
Pops! Pops!
[POPS]
Hm?
Spritle!
Go away! Don't try to come
in here. It's too dangerous!
[SPRITLE] Don't worry,
Pops. I like danger.
[SPRITLE grunts]
[SPEED, CURLY grunting]
Had enough yet?
[grunting, panting]
[sighs]
[SPEED]
The GRX...
[door clunks]
[SPEED]
I've got to try it. Just once.
[engine revs]
Sounds fabulous.
Powerful.
More than the Mach 5!
[engine revs]
[ALL]
Huh?!
[ALL gasp]
Look! It's Speed driving!
He shouldn't be driving it!
Even Speed can't respond quickly
enough for all that power!
--[horn honks]
--Huh?
[POPS]
Stop!
[horn honks]
Hey!
--[GOON 2 groans]
--[SPRITLE grunts]
I've got to stop Speed before
that GRX gets the best of him!
He's going so fast now,
we'll never able to catch him.
And if he's not careful,
he'll smash up!
I've never driven
so fast in my life!
[laughs]
[SPEED gasps]
[SPEED] This speed's taking
me into another dimension!
It's fantastic!
Another dimension!
I-I can't grasp it!
A dimension born of speed!
[sighs]
He's moving so fast;
I can hardly see him!
That car's going to
mean the end of him!
[NARRATOR] Speed is
unconscious at the wheel
of the fastest car on Earth.
How long before
its inevitable crash?
Don't miss the next thrilling
episode of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪