♪
♪ Here he comes,
here comes Speed Racer ♪
♪ He's a demon on wheels ♪
♪ He's a demon and he's gonna
be chasing after someone ♪
♪ He's gaining on you
so you better look alive ♪
♪ He's busy revving up
the powerful Mach 5 ♪
♪ And when the odds
are against him ♪
♪ And there's dangerous
work to do ♪
♪ You bet your life Speed Racer
will see it through ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ He's off and flying as he
guns the car around the track ♪
♪ He's jamming down the pedal
like he's never coming back ♪
♪ Adventure's waiting
just ahead ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
[ANNOUNCER]
Stand by, ladies and gentlemen!
The race is about to start!
Drivers, stand by
for the signal!
On your marks... Get ready...
It seems strange, Speed, to
see you up here in the stands
instead of in the race.
It'll be a good opportunity for
me to watch the other drivers.
[ANNOUNCER]
Go!
[BOTH gasp]
Nobody's driving the cars!
[ALL gasping]
[MAN cackling]
[MAN]
Keep racing, spook cars!
Keep racing straight
to the castle!
The castle of Dr. Crepit!
[siren wailing]
[CITIZENS murmuring]
[CREPIT]
Another bad accident, eh?
We're going to be late
for the theatre.
We'd better take a taxi.
Taxi!
[BOTH]
Huh?
It's completely empty!
[cackles]
We're pursuing a
speeding taxi cab.
[OFFICER A]
Faster!
[OFFICER B]
I'll try!
[beeping]
[ATTENDANT] Hey! You can't leave
without paying for parking!
There's nobody
drivin' them! Empty!
[siren wailing]
[NARRATOR] Metropolitan
Police Headquarters.
Every car from the Exorbitant
Garage was driven away
but nobody was
behind the wheels?!
That's impossible, you hear? And
there's nothing funny about it!
[phone rings]
Hold on a minute!
Metropolitan Police.
A police car went over a
cliff while pursuing a taxi
with nobody behind the wheel?!
So far, we've gotten report that
48,000 cars have disappeared
with nobody driving them!
Chief, there's only
one person I know
who might be able to
get to the bottom of this.
[CHIEF]
Who?
It's Speed Racer.
[CHIEF]
Hmm.
Very well. Put him on the job.
I'll turn the whole
case over to him.
You know, Speed,
at the rate all those cars
have been disappearing,
pretty soon, there won't
be any left on the road!
Don't worry, Trixie.
I'll find out who's behind
it and put a stop to it.
You're a regular
Sherlock Holmes.
What d'you say, Chim Chim?
Why don't we solve the
mystery before Speed does
and surprise him?
We'll hide in the truck
and watch what goes on.
Come on, this way!
Now while we're hidden,
let's hope that somebody
steals the truck.
[BOTH gasp]
[TRIXIE]
Nobody's in that car!
[signal ringing]
[BOTH gasp]
[tires screech]
Now the car's nowhere in sight!
It can't be too far away!
I've gotta find it. I wonder
where it might've gone.
There are no other roads here,
so it must've taken this one.
Excuse me, did you see
a strange car pass here?
[CREPIT]
Strange car?
There was nobody
behind the wheel.
[CREPIT]
What's that?
Nobody was driving? Very funny!
[cackles]
That's peculiar. It must've
passed by this spot.
Are you implying that I'm
lying to you about the car?
No, of course not.
But tell me something, sir.
Aren't you the famous automotive
engineer, Dr. J.D. Crepit?
[CREPIT]
Dr. Crepit? Never heard of him.
[CREPIT chuckles]
I'm sure that was Dr. Crepit!
[TRIXIE]
Hmm...
But what would he be doing
way out here in the country?
[SPEED]
I don't know.
All I do know is that he
retired a few years ago
and lives in a sort
of castle somewhere.
[CREPIT] The famous Mach 5...
Soon, that will disappear, too.
We're moving, Chim Chim!
Somebody must've jumped
into the front of the truck!
I wonder who it could be!
[BOTH gasp]
[SPRITLE]
There's nobody behind the wheel,
but somebody's driving us!
[SPEED] It's no use.
We can't find that empty car.
Might as well give up for today.
[TRIXIE] Nobody was behind
the wheel of that truck!
Quick, Speed!
Maybe you can catch it!
[SPEED]
Hang on!
Spritle and Chim Chim!
What're you doing here?
I'll tell you later, Speed!
First, catch that truck!
All right, get in!
[BOTH laugh]
What's that funny-looking
building over there?
[SPEED gasps]
Look!
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Hooray! We got 'em!
[CHIM CHIM laughing]
Why'd you pull away like that?
The car started by itself!
Look, the gear shift's moving!
Trixie, the Mach 5's been
put under remote control
of some kind!
We're helpless!
[TRIXIE]
Oh, no!
Speed, what'll we do?!
[SPEED]
There's nothing we can do!
I'd better do something,
or we'll be roasted!
[SPRITLE] I can't bear
to look! Hurry, Speed!
[TRIXIE screams]
[SPEED] I can't find
the remote control unit!
What's this? This must be
what's controlling the Mach 5,
but I can't reach it!
[SPRITLE]
Chim Chim, try to get it!
[SPRITLE] Go ahead, Chim Chim!
Reach for it, quick!
Come on, rip it off! Hurry!
[SPEED] Grab it, Chim Chim!
We're counting on you!
We're getting closer
to the furnace!
Grab it, Chim Chim, quick!
[SPRITLE]
We're almost there! Quick!
[shrieks]
[SPEED gasping]
[SPEED]
Hang on!
--[TRIXIE gasps]
--[SPEED sighs]
Thanks, Chim Chim. You saved us!
You did a great job.
I'm proud of you, Chim Chim.
Who'd expect to find a field of
flowers in a place like this?
It's mighty peculiar.
They're certainly beautiful.
I'd love to pick some, Speed.
[SPEED]
We'd better get out of here!
The blades aren't
cutting. Why not?
I'm gonna find out.
The tree's made of
some kind of metal.
[SPEED]
Metal?
[SPRITLE]
Mm-hm!
How can a tree be metal?
[TRIXIE] I'm gonna
check all those flowers.
[gasps]
The flowers are
made of metal also!
[SPEED]
Huh?! No kidding!
Hard as it is to believe,
it's obvious that
everything in this whole place
must be made of metal.
[TRIXIE]
Let's look around!
[SPRITLE gasping]
[TRIXIE] Oh...
It's really amazing, Speed.
Look at the metal deer!
[ALL gasp]
[deer creaking]
Wow! Sounds rusty.
It needs some oil.
[gasps]
What a pretty little squirrel...
Come on. To Trixie.
Let me hold it a minute, Trixie!
[BOTH gasp]
[gibbering]
What is it, Chim Chim?
What's the matter?
Hmm? Ah! It's Chim Chim
made of metal!
[BOTH gasp]
[growls]
[laughing]
The castle's so big
and beautiful...
Oh, I wanna look through it!
Be careful, Trixie! We don't
know what's inside that castle!
It might be a trap!
Don't worry, Speed!
It's much too beautiful
to be anything dangerous!
I'm not afraid!
I'd better keep an
eye on Trixie...
[BOTH gasp]
Wow... How will we get inside?
[SPEED]
Careful.
[gasps]
[TRIXIE]
It's an amusement park!
[SPEED] It looks so weird.
There's no one there!
[BOTH gasp]
What a fabulous place!
We'll have a lot of fun-- Here!
[SPEED]
Huh?!
[SPRITLE]
Indians! Made of metal!
[SPEED]
Look out!
[gasps]
I was almost hit!
Here comes the roller coaster!
Huh?!
[shrieks]
[gasps]
[whirring]
[BOTH gasp]
[SPRITLE] A whole flight
of model airplanes!
Phew, I think I
got them all now.
[CREPIT]
No! You did not get them all!
I just decided to
give you a break!
[SPEED]
Dr. Crepit!
[gasps]
A giant! He must be
as big as the sky!
No, Spritle!
He's using a projector to
flash a picture of himself.
[CREPIT]
Speed!
Yes?
It's too bad that you
came here to my castle
because now you know
far too much about me.
I'm sure you'll go
straight to the police,
but that can't be allowed!
[laughs]
Dr. Crepit, why does a great
man like you smash cars?
What's the reason?
Why have you caused the
police so much trouble?
The metal from those smashed
cars has been remolded
and used to build my castle and
everything else around here.
I've turned those ugly cars
into objects of beauty!
[SPEED] But, Doctor,
you haven't answered me yet!
Why have you done
what you've done?!
[CREPIT] Because I hate cars!
And for a very good reason!
I'm getting my
revenge against them!
I lost my wife when
she was hit by a car
and my son was crippled.
Ever since then, I've been a
lonely, old man and I hate cars.
I'm wanna destroy
every one of 'em
so they won't cause
any more accidents!
The world managed all right
before cars were invented,
and I'm sure that now,
people can manage to get by
without them again.
Anyway, I hate cars, and
I hate those who drive them!
And so, I hate you,
and I'll destroy you!
[gasps]
Ow! Cut it out! Those toy
bullets hurt! Come on! Stop it!
[CREPIT]
I'll make every car and driver
pay for my son being
hurt by a car!
[SON] No, don't! Don't! No!
Don't hurt anyone, Papa!
[CREPIT] I want revenge for what
happened to your mother and you!
[CREPIT]
Revenge!
Papa, please, stop!
[CREPIT]
Get away!
He's operating the remote
control from there!
[TRIXIE]
Speed! More planes!
If we can smash the
remote controller,
we'll stop the attack!
[gasps]
[SPRITLE]
Help!
[SPEED]
Huh? That gives me an idea!
Papa, stop fighting!
Please, stop fighting!
[gasps]
[TRIXIE]
Speed!
[gasps]
[SON]
Please, Papa! No more! No, no!
Papa, put it down! Papa!
[SON]
Wait!
Please don't hit him! Please!
He didn't realize
what he was doing!
[CREPIT]
Son! You're standing!
[SPEED]
Huh?
[SON]
Huh...? Oh...
So I am...
Papa, my legs are all right!
I can walk after all!
I'm perfectly all right, Papa!
He was able to walk
all along, Doctor.
You're the one who kept him
in the chair all of the time.
[SON crying]
You were unable to
forgive that driver
for what happened years ago,
and so you kept your
eyes shut to reality
and your son paid for that.
[CREPIT]
Oh...
Forgive me, my son...
[INSPECTOR]
Come along, Dr. Crepit.
[CREPIT]
All right, Inspector.
Goodbye. Take care of
our home while I'm away.
[SON]
I will...
We'll keep an eye on
the boy, Dr. Crepit.
He'll be in good hands so you
won't have to worry about him.
[CREPIT]
Thank you.
Be a good boy while
I pay for my crimes.
And someday, I'll be home again.
Oh, Papa...
[SON cries]
Now, stop crying. Goodbye, Son.
Goodbye...
Papa!
[SON crying]
Stop crying.
It won't do any good.
And anyway, you have a lot of
work to do starting right now.
Work? What d'you mean?
Preparing the castle
and the amusement park
to be a place where
children from all over
can come and enjoy themselves.
You've gotta get rid
of the metal flowers
and plant real ones.
Throw away the big metal trees
and make real ones grow.
Turn this place into a
place of natural beauty.
It'll be a lot of work,
but it'll be worth it.
I can see where I just won't be
able to sit by. I wanna help.
Me, too! And Chim Chim!
[CHIM CHIM gibbers]
You know... Papa is
gonna be very proud.
[NARRATOR]
Don't miss the next
exciting episode
of Speed Racer !
♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer
Go, Speed Racer ♪
♪ Go, Speed Racer, go! ♪