(birds cawing)
(suspenseful music)
(door clicks)
(wheels creaking)
(piano creaks)
(suspenseful music)
(note plays)
(Ghost laughs)
(singing in a foreign language)
(chilling music)
(whimsical music)
(wind blows)
(Satsuki screams)
- Sweet, it looks like a little
peppermint panty wonderland.
- You open that window again
and I'm gonna push you out of it.
- If I were you,
I wouldn't wear horizontal
stripes like that,
it makes your butt look big.
- I'll kill you!
(Hajime laughs)
- You'll have to catch me first, fat ass!
- Come back here, you coward!
- If you lose weight, you'd move faster!
- Hold it right there.
- [Hajime] Oh, the music
teacher, what a bitch.
- How would you like a trip
to the principal's office?
- [ Satsuki] Not too much.
- I didn't think you would.
Now remember this little moment
when you vote for teacher of the year.
- Bush one, bush two, you're
not getting my vote either.
- Good girl.
Now you and your future delinquent friend
can help me carry some boxes.
Dammit, where'd the beast go?
- What?
I hate him.
- [Music Teacher] You're strong.
I'm gonna have to remember
that when I move offices.
- Hopefully offices in another school.
- I'm sorry, what?
- You're pretty.
- Thanks?
All right, let's go.
- Fine.
- [Music Teacher] Matthew
Greenfield and little Donny Rush,
- Awe, man.
- I expelled you two last week!
Come back here!
You take those boxes
inside, I'll be right back.
- What?
- [Music Teacher] If
Gin Chung is here too,
you're in big trouble!
(birds cawing)
(ominous music)
- [Satsuki] Subtle, nice.
Why don't you just draw a target on me?
(floor creaking)
(wind blows)
The music room, the music room.
(distant crashing)
(Satsuki gasps)
(Satsuki giggles)
Girl alone in haunted
school house, I'm an idiot.
(suspenseful music)
- [Ghost] Do you have any
books written by black people?
Yeah.
("Für Elise" begins)
(floor creaks)
("Für Elise" continues)
(Satsuki breaths deeply)
(floor creaks)
(music intensifies)
(door rumbles)
("Für Elise" continues)
(Satsuki whimpers softly)
(floor creaking)
(piano creaks)
(Satsuki breathes heavily)
(suspenseful music)
(muted piano note taps)
(Satsuki whimpers)
(Satsuki cries)
(door shuts)
(piano key plays)
(ominous laughter)
- [Ghost] Three more times.
(piano bangs)
- [All] What?
- You mean you actually heard it?
Get out.
- It's the piano ghost of the music room,
all the kids are talking about it,
that and the head cheerleader
getting pregnant, big story.
- Piano ghost, what?
- [Hajime] If you hear
him playing, you die,
like the Ring and that tape,
or something else from Japan.
- What?
- [Leo] To put it accurately,
a person who hears the music
piece the piano ghost plays,
"Für Elise", four times all
the way through will die
and the cheerleader is carrying twins.
- [Hajime] I think the tempo
changes each time you hear it,
that's when you know you're screwed,
or he's just getting tired.
- I also heard that during
the fourth performance,
the music piece is played
with a mercilessly slow pace.
- I see, at least it's
not Creed's Greatest Hits.
(thud)
- [Hajime] Scott Stapp rocks!
- Don't yell at me!
I'm gonna die, I have
enough pressure on me!
- [Keichirrou] Are you gonna die?
(Keichirrou mumbles)
(Keichirrou cries)
- I'm just kidding, I'm
fine, I've got mom's diary.
(Satsuki whimpers)
There's nothing written about it here.
I am gonna die!
- [Leo] We all gotta go sometime.
- Perhaps when your
mother was still alive,
the piano ghost wasn't around.
You could be meeting your
savior sooner than you thought.
(Keichirrou sobs)
- Let me ask you something.
How about you not smile so
much when you're saying that?
- Oh, sorry about that.
- Poor Keiichirou, I
feel so sorry for him.
(Keichirrou cries)
- Hey, hold the phone a sec!
I'll be fine, all I have
to do is avoid hearing
that damn piano song for a couple of days.
I'm not a classical music fan anyway.
- [ Hajime] What's your plan exactly?
- Stay away from the school house.
So for the next couple of weeks,
it's Howard Stern, Rush
Limbo, and Paul Harvey
if he stays alive that long.
- Just stay away from Michael Savage.
- You're gonna die.
- [Satsuki] I'm not gonna die.
- [Keiichirou] Are you
sure you're not gonna die?
- Are you talking about the piano ghost?
(Keiichirou screams)
I'm sure I'll live a long, miserable life
of heartbreak and alcoholism
before a ghost takes me out.
- If you're lying, thank you.
(Keiichirou sobs)
- I told you I'm going to be fine.
Why are you still crying?
- Because (indistinct)
- Yeah.
- You think so too?
(Keiichirou sniffs)
Thanks, I thought it was just me.
- Goodnight.
- Goodnight, cowboy.
- He might have a good
night, but you won't.
- You shut the hell up.
I haven't fed you yet.
- [Cat] Heard any good
piano concertos lately?
(cat snickers)
(ominous music)
- I hate that cat.
(telephone rings)
Now telemarketers.
Milk Tan here!
That never gets old.
Hello?
(phone rings)
(ominous music continues)
(Satsuki grumbles)
(telephone rings)
(Satsuki groans)
At least give me some heavy
breathing or something.
("Für Elise" begins)
(Satsuki gasps)
("Für Elise" continues)
(phone clicks)
(Satsuki gasps)
(telephone button clicks)
(music quickens)
(Satsuki whimpers)
(telephone button clicks)
Disconnecting.
(Satsuki sobs)
(telephone clatters)
(Satsuki grunts)
(Satsuki yells)
(music begins)
What?
(piano music continues)
(Satsuki whimpers)
(door bangs)
(music continues)
(Satsuki whimpers)
(door slams)
(Satsuki breaths deeply)
(Satsuki sighs)
(distorted beep)
("Für Elise"" begins)
(Satsuki whimpers)
Ah!
(batteries clatter)
(Satsuki pants)
(""Für Elise"" continues)
Oh, please!
(Satsuki whimpers)
(Satsuki groans)
(Satsuki cries)
(Satsuki sighs)
Oh man, I wish I was deaf.
(toy creaks)
- [Ghost] Two more times
(ghost laughs)
- [Hajime] For real?
- [Satsuki] Yeah for real.
- If you listen to "Für Elise"
two more times, that's it.
- You promised you
weren't gonna die, liar.
(Keiichirou sobs)
- Keiichirou fear not.
The Lord God is with thee.
- [Keiichirou] What do you know?
- And God will wipe away
every tear from their eyes,
Revelations 21:4.
- What are you gonna do now?
Obviously you are staying away
from the schoolhouse only talk radio plan
isn't gonna cut it.
- And apparently,
the ghost's musical delivery
system isn't limited
to piano playing.
The song could come from anywhere.
- Hey how about you stuff
cotton or clay in your ears?
- [Satsuki] Shut up.
- Fine, die, see if I care.
- Hey, that's it.
I must have been preoccupied
with the cheerleader story.
I should have thought of it.
- [Satsuki] I don't think so.
- They're not what you think they are,
they're ear plugs.
Just shove them in when
you hear the piano.
Or Momoko (indistinct).
- [Teacher] Take this triangle ABC.
- From point A,
(Hajime yawns)
draw a perpendicular line down to line BC.
We'll call this line Suzie.
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music begins)
- [Ghost] Two more times.
(Ghost chuckles)
- [Leo] If you listen
to "Für Elise" two more times, that's it.
Just shove 'em in when you hear the piano.
Or Momoko (indistinct).
(door knocks)
(Satsuki gasps)
(ominous music intensifies)
(doorknob creaks)
(Satsuki screams)
- What in the world are you doing, Satski?
You got a phone call.
He says his name is Leo.
Is he your boyfriend?
(Dad laughs)
- Dad, don't be gross!
What is it, Leo?
- [Ghost] Yes, it's me Leo.
After doing some checking
on the piano ghost,
I discovered some new facts.
- What?
What new facts?
- [Ghost] Oh, the facts.
Well, we probably shouldn't
discuss it over the phone.
Hey, I've got an idea.
Why don't you come to the
scary isolated payphone
on the bad side of town alone, yeah.
- Okay, give me a minute.
(phone dial tone)
(ominous music)
(crickets chirp)
- Come on Leo.
Matter of life or death here.
("Für Elise" begins)
(wheels squeak)
(Satsuki whimpers)
Oh!
("Für Elise" continues)
What?
Where'd you get these things?
The dollar store?
(Satsuki pants)
All I need to do is not
hear the whole song.
Then I'll be fine.
I'll have to run all the way to Asaka,
but at least I'll be alive.
(Satski pants)
God, this is what I get
for skipping PE class
and now look what (indistinct) happened.
(Satsuki pants)
(music plays)
Ah!
(music intensifies)
(Satsuki screams)
(Satsuki pants)
(music continues)
Ah!
Crap.
(wheels squeak)
(music continues)
(piano rumbles)
(Satsuki screams)
(piano music fades)
(haunting music)
(Satsuki screams)
(music continues)
No!
(doorbell rings)
- Hello?
Who is it?
Oh, it's you.
You're still alive.
Lighten up, it's just a joke.
Oh crap, I'll get my coat.
(ominous music begins)
- [Hajime] Everyone, all set?
- [Leo] Lock and load.
- [Momoko] Be strong in the
Lord and the power of his might.
- [Leo] That ghost was impersonating me!
Well of course he was, I'm the best actor.
- Thank you.
- Don't sweat it, baby.
Toss me a couple pairs of
those panties and we're even.
Now let's rock and roll!
- Play ball!
(ominous music)
- [Satsuki] What's the plan?
- We find the music room
and go all Rachmaninoff
on his ass.
If we smash his piano,
he can't play now can he?
(Hajime shouts)
(items rattle)
Dammit, who left a stupid box in the hall?
Oh no, my bike headlight.
- This must be the place.
("Für Elise" begins)
- It's the piano ghost!
- [Hajime] All right, let's go!
- A Steinway.
- Yes, but there's no one playing it.
- All right, knock it off
you cheap shot show pan.
If you're not gonna play Tori Amos,
you got no business at those keys.
Ah!
(Hajime yells)
(Hajime scream)
(Hajime groans)
- [All] Hajime!
- Oh man, that really hurt!
- It's a force field.
If they're anything like the
ones I've seen on Star Trek,
Satski's a goner.
This is so sad.
- What?
As friends, you guys suck.
(foreign language) do something.
- I'm not gonna let you die.
- [Momoko] Good.
- I got a couple pair of
panties riding on this.
- Good luck, Hajime.
(Hajime screams)
Oh good job.
If I thought you were gonna half-ass it,
I would have made Leo go do it.
- I'm not gonna let some
out of tune Tchaikovsky
get the best of me, shut up.
- The recital's almost over.
I'd hustle if I were you.
- I'll go in first again.
You guys follow.
Got it?
( Hajime yells)
- Bang bang.
- Batter up!
- God protect us.
- Go get em.
(all groan)
(Keiichirou screams)
- Keiichirou!
Try it again!
- Man down.
- [Hajime] Well this plan isn't working.
Anyone got any bright ideas?
- [Leo] I'm thinking.
- [Hajime] Think faster!
- [Leo] Stop yelling, I can't concentrate!
- [Hajime] Come on Mr.
Psychical researcher.
- [Leo] Oh, don't start that again.
- The piano's not it I'm afraid.
The real piano ghost is there!
(music intensifies)
- A portrait of Antonio Banderas?
- So all we need to do
is destroy the painting,
is that what you're saying?
- The metronome.
- Huh?
- Look for a damn metronome, you nitwit.
- [Leo] Gotcha, let's look.
- That's what that damn clicking thing was
in that stupid box.
- I got your back.
(door slams)
Hey, what's the big idea?
- Come on, you little weakling.
Pull.
- Look out Keiichirou, behind you!
- What?
Ah!
(Keiichirou screams)
(ominous music intensifies)
- There, you owe me one.
And as for you, take that and that.
- What?
- Oh no.
- Hurry!
Hurry children, he'll start
playing "Für Elise" again.
(Hajime grunts)
(ghost moans)
- Here it is!
- Get back.
Ah!
(Satsuki screams)
- Look out!
- Now only one more phrase.
("Für Elise" continues)
(Satsuki screams)
- Sleep here, oh ghost,
to spiritual sleep.
(Ghost gasps)
(metronome ticks)
(Ghost moans)
(metronome ticking continues)
- It's not stopping.
- Hurry, they're only a few
more notes left in the piece.
- It's past your bed time!
(Ghost screams)
- Kick his ass.
(Ghost moans)
(Ghost screams)
(metronome ticks)
- God, thanks.
That guy was terrible.
- Hasta la vista, baby.
(all sigh)
- Satsuki, hey what's the matter?
- Man down.
- [Hajime] For crying out loud,
we do all the work and she's
the one who passes out?
Lame.
- [Momoko] She was so
frightened of the ghost,
she probably didn't get
any sleep last night.
- [Leo] Hey Momoko,
lemme ask you something.
How did you know how to put
that ghost into spiritual sleep?
- Oh, don't give me any credit.
- It was all the Lord Jesus.
- Okay, whatever.
How did the Lord Jesus tell
you how to put it to sleep?
- Not me, I was just an
instrument of the Lord,
though I'm a little fuzzy on the details.
- [Hajime] I don't
understand it but it worked,
so I'm cool.
- [Leo] She's not answering my questions.
She's not helping.
- If you really wanna help
you could help carry her,
she's fatter then she looks.
- [Leo] If you really wanna help.
(gentle music)
(singing in foreign language)
- [Satsuki] What?
The school's sports day is being canceled?
There's a boy who's practicing
with everything he's got.
- [Woman] All he wanted to do was run.
- [Boy] I just, I just wanted to run.