(wind whistling)
(door creaking)
- Hey, is someone here?
(clock tolling)
(light bulb crackling)
Hey, quit messing around!
(eerie rattling)
(eerie whooshing)
(man gasping)
(eerie music)
- [Ghostly Voice] Behind you.
(man screaming)
(singer singing in Japanese)
(energetic upbeat music)
(ominous music)
(bright upbeat music)
- Hey, there it is!
(truck rumbling)
Is that the new school we'll go to?
- You know, a long time ago
your grandmother was the principal here
and this is actually the place
where your mother and I first met.
- I kinda like the old school better.
(Kaya meowing)
- No no, you're looking
at the old schoolhouse,
the school you two are gonna
be going to is next door.
- [Both] Huh?
- [Keiichirou] Awesome,
it's a brand new building!
- That's great!
I was kinda worried there
weren't gonna be any,
you know, modern bathrooms.
- So you were scared too then, huh?
- Well, I wasn't scared exactly.
(eerie whooshing)
- [Keiichirou] Whatcha lookin' at?
- [Reiichirou] Satsuki, get back in here,
you'll get your head cut off!
- [Satsuki] Oh, Dad, you worry too much!
(eerie whooshing)
- [Reiichirou] Put that in the back room.
- [Mover] You got it.
- The rest of them will be all right,
the movers will take
care of it, don't worry.
- Why you wanna live in your dead wife's
old house is beyond me.
It's sick, you're sick!
- Wow, Dad!
Grandpa, this place is so big!
Can we go upstairs?
- Sure but don't bother them.
- Yeah!
- When this bitch kicks,
I'm moving to Vegas.
(Reiichirou chuckling)
- Wow, all ready for us to move in!
- Wow, hey!
You think it's okay if we
make this our game room?
- Well, let's ask Dad about it later.
(Satsuki chuckling)
- Ooh, white panties!
(Satsuki yelping)
(Satsuki screaming)
Yo, my name's Hajime.
You're the new transfer
student, aren't you?
- Yes, but it's none of your business!
I guess you're the new pervert?
- Whatever!
I was here first you know!
Listen, you flashed me, remember that!
- [Reiichirou] Satsuki, Keiichirou?
Help me with your mother, will you?
- [Both] Okay!
- Just grab her picture.
- Okay.
Bleh!
- So she doesn't have a mother.
Sad!
(traffic humming)
(birds chirping)
(students chattering)
- You sure you both are okay?
- [Satsuki] It'll be all
right, don't worry about us!
Just don't be late for
your first day of work.
- I won't.
Now remember you two,
just say no to everything.
- [Satsuki] Okay.
- [Both] Goodbye, Daddy!
- All right, Keiichirou-
- Hey!
- Out with it!
Ah-ha!
(Kaya meowing)
(sighing) Why did you bring him with you?
- Well, because I don't
have any friends here yet.
The teacher's gonna get mad at you.
Take him back-
(Kaya meowing)
Hey!
- Kaya!
- Kaya, no!
(Kaya meowing)
Kaya!
(leaves rustling)
(birds chirping)
- Hey, there he is!
(Kaya meowing)
- He went in the old schoolhouse.
Let's go.
(wind whooshing)
(both screaming)
It, it, it was just the wind, yeah.
(eerie tense music)
(eerie whooshing)
(Keiichirou babbling)
(Satsuki gulping)
(eerie whooshing)
There's nothing to be
afraid of, Keiichirou,
monsters only get evil
people like Republicans
and we're not old enough to vote!
(doors slamming)
(both screaming)
(boys yelling)
(Satsuki and Keiichirou screaming)
- White again! Well!
(boys snickering)
- [Satsuki] (sobbing) Pervert!
- Well, I've been called worse than that.
- You're stalking me.
- You flatter yourself way too much, baby.
Look, I just came here
to give you a warning
and that's all I came here for.
- What warning?
- No trespassing in the old
schoolhouse, with good reason.
- But Kaya came in here.
- What's a Kaya?
- It's our cat, idiot.
Now be a good neighbor
and help us look for him.
- No thanks, I'm getting
the hell outta here!
(Hajime yelping)
- What's your problem?
We're just looking for our cat.
(eerie whooshing)
- Well, this place is haunted.
- [Both] Huh?
- Allow the school's
top psychical researcher
to explain it to you.
Oh, the name's Leo by the way.
You see the numerous-
- Don't be stupid!
Just because we're new to town
doesn't mean we're from the sticks.
- I hear non-believers tend
to get targeted even more.
They come after you and
get you from behind!
(Satsuki gasping)
What, what is it?
(eerie whooshing)
(Hajime and Leo yelping)
- I'm sorry.
I didn't scare you, did I?
(Hajime and Leo sighing)
- You're an older classman.
- Giggity-giggity.
- Oh, there's no need to apologize.
I'm the one who's just moved to town,
I should be introducing myself to you!
I'm Satsuki Manshita.
- Manshita?
- That's right.
- Hm, I'm Momoko, I think I'm
in the class ahead of you.
- Really? A little older?
How do you do?
- Not too good, actually.
That big gust of wind blew my hat off.
It flew in here, I came to find it.
(air whooshing)
- I can help!
- Yes, why don't you let us
look for your hat for you?
- Oh, that's so nice of you!
- [Hajime] Allow me to
introduce myself, I'm Hajime.
- [Leo] And my name is, uh, call me Leo.
- [Momoko] Hi, Leo.
- Okay, you'll find a hat but not a cat?
- [Hajime] Mind your own
business, panty girl!
Now I believe you said it flew in here?
Don't be afraid, Momoko, it's all right,
I'm right here with you.
- [Leo] Yeah, and, uh, me too.
- You're such brave, strong, handsome men.
Have you accepted Jesus
as your personal savior?
- No, I'm Jewish.
- I just wanna make
sure that you're saved.
I am and ever since I was
saved I've had the gifts
and I can sense this place is haunted.
As a matter of fact, I
feel a very strong sense
of evil right now, just around the corner.
(floorboards creaking)
(eerie music)
(Leo screaming)
(all except Momoko screaming)
- It's that the statue
of Kinjiro Ninomiya?
- Why, yes it is, and he
looks really cute in my hat.
(blow thudding)
(Leo yelping)
- You stupid idiot!
The only thing that scared me
was you screaming like little girl!
Ass.
- But wasn't that statue
outside a while ago?
(eerie whooshing)
(all yelping)
- Christ!
(all screaming)
- Run!
(all panting)
- Sweet Jesus, that was scary!
- Yeah, moving statues are.
- The stories of paranormal-
- Here.
- Activity in the old-
- God bless you!
- Schoolhouse are true!
- Hey, Hardy Boy, let's
just get outta here.
- [Keiichirou] We can't
leave, Kaya's still-
- I don't care about your
cat, he's probably dead.
- Shut up!
(Keiichirou sobbing)
Kaya's a very special cat!
Kaya just showed up on the
day of our mother's funeral.
Our dead mother!
You feel bad now?
- I can only hope she knew about Jesus.
- But what if you're-
(Kaya meowing)
- Hey, it's Kaya!
- [Satsuki] Dead mother!
- [Hajime] Oh, all right.
- [Leo] But...
(water dripping)
- Kaya!
(Kaya meowing)
Where are you?
(tense spooky music)
(Kaya meowing)
- There he is!
- What's the matter?
What is it, Kaya?
(dog snarling)
- [Keiichirou] Uh-oh!
- So that's why he's afraid.
- It's just a stupid dog.
- But what's a dog doing-
- Hey dog, leave our cat alone
he didn't do anything to you!
- In the old schoolhouse?
- Shut up!
Who you calling a dog?
- What the hell?
- Oh my goodness!
- Kids!
(eerie whooshing)
(Kaya meowing)
- Kaya, come back!
Let's follow him!
- [Leo] What if we meant
to follow our own path?
(door rattling)
- [Satsuki] Kaya?
- Fear not, the Lord God is with thee.
- But someone else isn't!
- That's the girl's restroom
and I don't have to go.
- I do have to go, but I'm
pee shy so I need my privacy.
- Shut up and get inside!
- Bully.
- They say Hanako the
Bathroom Ghost live here.
- In the name of Jesus-
- What are you doing?
Will you stop that?
- [Momoko] I'm casting her out.
- Yes?
(all except Momoko yelping)
(door creaking)
(air whistling)
- It worked, wow.
- [Satsuki] When you
gotta go, you gotta go!
- [Hajime] Huh?
- What should we play today?
(Hajime and Leo screaming)
(engine revving)
(dramatic music)
(both screaming)
(motorcycle whooshing)
- What? What did we miss?
- He, he needs some head.
- And I don't wanna find out why.
Please, God, can we go now?
(eerie chittering)
- I wanna go home now.
(Keiichirou sobbing)
(eerie chittering)
(all screaming)
(bucket clanging)
(Hajime yelping)
(all grunting)
(all crashing)
- Huh?
(eerie chittering)
Ah?
(all sighing)
- Oh, Hallelujah.
- I remember now.
I read in a book once that when
being chased by a Teke Teke,
you should crawl down
onto the ground, yeah.
(blow thudding)
(Leo yelping)
- You could've shared that with
the class a little earlier!
Come on, let's get out
of this stupid place.
Oh no.
(doorknob rattling)
- What's the matter?
- What do you think's the matter?
- We're locked in?
Help, somebody help!
(Keiichirou sobbing)
Is anyone out there?
- I haven't even
bar mitzvahed yet.
- Hey, somebody open
the damn door!
- Dear Lord.
- Somebody please help us!
(Keiichirou babbling)
- [Hajime] Not in my ear, please.
- Shut up.
- Is that you, Lord?
- [Leo] I can't take it anymore!
- [Hajime] Would you get a
hold of yourself, you big baby?
- We're not alone.
(eerie laughing)
(Satsuki gasping)
Huh?
(ghost laughing)
What is that?
(pensive music)
- A really ugly ghost?
- Obviously a demon straight
from the pit of hell.
(camera clicking)
- Let's you and I be friends, Satsuki.
- What? You gotta be kidding me!
- Dead mother, you're
lonely, you need a friend!
- No orphan's that lonely!
- Believe it, you'd rather have me
as a friend than an enemy.
(eerie whooshing)
(chandelier crashing)
(all yelping)
(ghost laughing)
- No way!
(cabinet crashing)
(Leo yelping)
(glass shattering)
(Satsuki yelping)
(Keiichirou babbling)
(ghost snickering)
- Okay, and now it's a bigger ugly ghost.
- Come on, Satsuki, let's be friends.
- Me and you friends?
(Keiichirou sobbing)
- Hello!
(objects crashing)
- Look out!
(umbrellas whooshing)
(Satsuki yelping)
(umbrellas crashing)
(Keiichirou babbling)
- This friend deal is off.
(ghost cackling)
(grim music)
- [Hajime] Oh crap!
- Who'd wanna be friends with you anyway?
Especially after the grudge
I've held against you for years!
- But I just met you.
- Keiichirou, do you
know the sinner's prayer?
- I believe its size is
increasing in direct proportion
to our rising level of fear, yeah.
- Keiichirou, don't be afraid!
(Satsuki gasping)
(ghost snarling)
(Keiichirou whimpering)
(ghost roaring)
(all screaming)
- [Ghost] Look at you run!
- I said don't be afraid!
- Why the hell would I listen to you?
(all panting)
(Keiichirou panting)
Close the door!
- [Ghost] Where are you?
(suspenseful music)
(all sighing)
(Kaya meowing)
- This is the principal's office.
(Satsuki gasping)
Kaya!
Principals always look like lesbians.
Mom?
No, it can't be!
- And this is actually the place
where your mother and I first met.
- I heard they looked alike
but I didn't think they
looked this much alike.
- What is that?
(Kaya meowing)
- Well-
- She looks like-
- Careful!
- No, that picture.
When I volunteered at the wonderful
Exodus Homosexual Conversion Camp,
I met this woman who was there who looked
a lot like that lesbian, I mean woman.
- By any chance, you don't
remember what her name was?
- Kayako?
- That's our mother!
- What?
I'm so sorry.
I mean, praise God.
- No way!
- What a blessed coincidence
from the Lord, amen.
- I think it's not coincidence.
I mean, maybe Mom is kind
of bringing us all together.
- What's a lesbian?
(Keiichirou gasping)
(ghost cackling)
- [Ghost] Found you!
(wall crashing)
(all screaming)
(tense dramatic music)
- Take that!
(Hajime grunting)
- Why won't it break?
- [Ghost] You won't be able to leave here
for the rest of your lives!
(all screaming)
(ghost laughing)
(Keiichirou babbling)
Gee, aren't we friends?
- No, we're goners!
- Hey, this is that ghost.
- Satan.
- [Hajime] Shut up, it says Amanojaku.
- "March 15th, the Amanojaku appeared.
"When I enclosed a flame
inside a magic circle
"and began chanting
'Jaku, Jaku, go to sleep,'
"It went into the big camphor tree
"on the mountain behind the school."
- [Momoko] She bound it
in the name of Jesus.
- That's one way of putting
it, spiritual sleep is another.
- [Hajime] So if we do the same
thing that's written there,
then we can put that ghost to sleep!
- [Amanojaku] (cackling) This is fun!
- Let's just try it!
I'll go draw the magic circle, yeah.
- Or a cross?
- (gasping) The science room!
We need to go to the science room.
- That's right, they've
got Bunsen burners!
(air warbling)
- You can't escape!
(Momoko yelping)
(intense music)
- Is this enough?
- No, why don't you knock down a wall?
Yes, it's fine!
(Keiichirou babbling)
- Got it!
- It's done, yeah!
(wall crashing)
(Amanojaku roaring)
- Get inside the magic circle!
That's not a Bunsen burner!
- [Hajime] What do you want from me?
(table crashing)
(Keiichirou screaming)
- Lord, forgive me for
this satanic ritual.
(Amanojaku chuckling)
(Keiichirou yelling)
(grim suspenseful music)
- Got it!
- Let's start the magic spell.
(Amanojaku roaring)
- [All] Jaku, Jaku, go to sleep!
Jaku, Jaku, go to sleep!
(Amanojaku groaning)
(all yelling)
(Amanojaku grunting)
(triumphant music)
- [Amanojaku] No!
- [All] Jaku, Jaku, go to sleep!
Jaku, Jaku, go to sleep!
(Amanojaku yelling)
- [Amanojaku] That book!
No!
(Amanojaku groaning)
- [All] Jaku, Jaku, go to sleep!
Jaku, Jaku, go to sleep!
(Amanojaku yelling)
(Keiichirou babbling)
(Kaya meowing)
- Is it gone?
(all groaning)
- [Leo] Looks like the spell worked.
- We did it.
We got rid of him, we did it!
- Thanks to that somewhat satanic book.
- I guess you're right,
but why was this inside a picture frame?
It's Mom!
- What?
- Mom's name is written
right inside of it!
"Fifth Grade, Group One, Kayako Kamiyama,"
that was mom's name
before she married Dad!
(Keiichirou babbling)
(somber music)
That's right, Keiichirou,
Mom's looking after us,
even from heaven.
(Keiichirou sobbing)
(Keiichirou babbling)
- [Leo] Thank goodness we're outside.
- [Hajime] I'm never going back
in the old schoolhouse again.
Ever. Ever!
(school bell chiming)
- Oh, the bell.
- The school bell.
School bell?
- Oh no, we're late!
Let's go!
- But wait!
But we were only in the old-
- It's time
to leave school-
- schoolhouse for 20 minutes.
- Students still on campus-
- Was the magic space
trapped in time?
- Please leave immediately.
- [PA Announcer] I repeat,
it is time to leave school.
Students who are still on-
- I don't suppose any of you-
- Campus, please leave-
- Can come up with
a believable excuse?
- School immediately.
- Skipping my first day
of class, I'm screwed!
- Who's gonna believe us?
We missed a whole day of class
because of paranormal activity!
(all except Momoko sighing)
- My friends, today we
answered to a higher calling.
We bound an evil spirit
and placed it back in
the big camphor tree.
Hallelujah!
- Hey!
- Oh, what is it now?
- Leo, didn't they chop
down the big camphor tree
on the mountain the
other day, or am I high?
- You're not high.
Not only was the camphor
tree chopped down,
the whole mountain site is being turned
into residential developments!
- Well, then where's that stupid ghost,
inside one of those condos?
- How would I know?
- Well, he better be gone,
because if he's not he's
gonna be pissed off!
- Oh I'm pissed off all right!
(all gasping)
(Keiichirou babbling)
(suspenseful music)
- [All] Amanojaku!
- [Leo] Duck and cover!
- But where,
where's he coming from?
- Where are you?
(Keiichirou whimpering)
(Amanojaku cackling)
- I'm here.
Don't think you've gotten the best of me!
It's gonna take a lot more than
five prepubescent
pipsqueaks to get rid of me!
In fact, I'll drag all the
children in this school
into a world of fear and
get my ghostly powers back!
What are you looking at?
I'll strike you down with my...
What the hell?
What the hell did you brats do to me?
- He's in our damn cat.
- What kind of trick is this?
Wait til I get my hands on you!
- [Leo] A case of
demonic possession, yeah.
- What are you looking at?
Go away or I'll turn you
into a toad or a snake!
- Black cats have always been evil.
- I got an idea!
Why don't you just kill the cat
and that will release my spirit
and I can go back to haunting that school!
- Not an option, but neutering is!
- Of all the forms that
could be banished into,
this is the worst!
I'm gonna make you pay for this, girly!
- Hey there, what are you kids doing here?
School's over!
Go home, you sillies!
- Oh, thanks!
- Oh, nice cat!
(Amanojaku meowing)
(Keiichirou babbling)
(tense music)
- [Man] Yeah, such a pretty cat.
- That jerk, pretending to be our cat!
- Don't make him mad!
It's no use, we'll just have
to keep an eye on things
until we find a way to turn
your cat back to normal.
- [Satsuki] Well, that blows!
- Interesting, the mountain
where everyone written about
in that diaries is spiritual sleep.
Two generations of your family
have stolen my freedom
and ruined my plans.
You'll pay for this!
(singer singing in Japanese)
♪ I miss you, I miss you ♪
♪ I need you, I need you ♪
♪ Sexy, sexy ♪
(eerie upbeat music)
(singer singing in Japanese)
♪ Come back, come back, come back ♪
♪ Sexy, sexy ♪
- [Hajime] What?
The toilet at the old schoolhouse?
- [Leo] As a matter of fact,
it looks like a teacher
fell victim too, yeah.
- [Satsuki] Hajime, I'm
sorry, I can't do it!
(air whooshing)
- [Hajime] Satsuki!