[TENGAN] Ladies and gentlemen,
Hope's Peak has been liberated.
And why are rescue
teams not on the scene?
[OPERATOR A] First responders
just arrived, sir.
So... Junko Enoshima.
[YUKIZOME]
I, uh...
I'm sorry. This is my fault.
I was sure she wasn't
behind all this.
I won't tell you not
to let it sting.
That said, this just goes to
show how formidable she was.
[YUKIZOME]
Kyosuke.
[growls]
[TENGAN]
Finally, the door is open.
[MUNAKATA]
So you, of all people,
figured out who the Attacker is.
Munakata, please.
We owe it to her to listen.
Where's the harm in that?
Start talking.
Go on.
Right, yes.
Well, these are all the
notes Kyoko had made
up to this point, and...
Yeah. There. Have a look.
[NAEGI] "The only latent prints
found at any of the crime scenes
have been from the
victims themselves.
Stab wounds are situated in
easily accessible areas
of the body.
In other words..."
Suicide?
"...is the only logical
conclusion that fits the facts."
She can't've been serious!
You see? Nobody was
actually murdered.
That's insanity! Why would
they've killed themselves?
What could possibly have
pushed them over the edge?
Let me see that for a minute.
[NAEGI] She made a map
of the rooms showing
where the victims were found,
where the survivors stayed,
and the monitors.
[ASAHINA] So you think there's
some kind of connection?
[NAEGI]
Uh...
Now that you mention it,
there has to be.
One was there.
In fact, I think that's true
of every crime scene.
Yeah, whenever we
found a victim,
there was always a monitor.
Of course, that doesn't explain
the role they played.
Hmm...
All right, Munakata.
I have a proposition.
[ASAHINA]
I'd like to go on record
saying this is a terrible idea.
I get what you're doing,
but if you're right,
you're dead!
It'll all be fine, Asahina.
Why else do you think I'd have
Munakata tie me up like this?
Still not the most
foolproof plan.
Hey, guys, we're almost
at the, uh, time limit.
Look, whatever you
expect to get out of this,
just swear to me Kyoko's death
hasn't pushed you past
some kind of breaking
point, okay?
[chuckles]
She'd be pissed at me if it had.
I would never dishonor
her memory like that.
She looked for the truth.
Nothing kept her from searching.
She held out hope
till the bitter end.
After all, if she could do it,
then I'd darn-well
better, right?
And plus...
What?
I made a promise to
my little sister.
I told her I'd come and get
her once this was all over.
[NAEGI]
So, yeah.
I intend to be a survivor.
[music plays]
[MUNAKATA]
Suicide.
But if he's just
grasping at straws...
[ASAHINA]
Naegi.
[beeping]
[MONOKUMA]
Top o' the morning to ya!
Wakey-wakey, eggs and bakey!
Attacker! Come out,
come out wherever you are!
Yep, it's time to work
your bloody magic.
Who shall be the
target for today?
Ah! Well bust my buttons,
it's you! "What? There must..."
That's how it's done.
The bangles. They wake you up
when you're near a monitor.
What's going on?
What are you planning?
[MONOKUMA] ... what everyone
in your position says.
C'mon. Being the
Attacker ain't that bad.
Get-Get-Get this!
Believe it or not...
This isn't live.
It's a recording.
[MONOKUMA] Hm? Eager to
find out what it is?
Sure you are. That's
what I like about you.
Now, pay close attention.
[music playing]
Naegi.
[KIRIGIRI]
You're still alive.
Naegi.
[NAEGI gasps]
You're such a liar.
Remember you swore to get me
out alive? What happened there?
[KIRIGIRI]
This is all your fault.
B-But I--!
I'm sorry. I don't
understand why you're--
Why are you still alive, Naegi?
Yeah, right? You're the
one who deserves to die.
[KIRIGIRI, MAIZONO]
Naegi.
It should've been you who
was killed instead of us.
[NAEGI]
But I--
[NAEGI] I-I just wanted
everyone to be...
[NAEGI]
To be...
No. Wait. Please!
[NAEGI cries]
[screaming]
That's the way. Join us, Naegi.
Yes, yes. Join us.
[BOTH]
Do it, Naegi!
Sure. On my way.
[thud]
[NAEGI]
Uh...?
[JUZO] You're the man who
defeated Junko Enoshima.
If you think I'm gonna
let you kill yourself,
you're dumber than you look!
Hear me, ya little punk?
Not now. Not ever!
How are you even--?
You wanna die so bad, allow me.
[clatter]
[JUZO]
Damn it.
[NAEGI]
How-How are you still awake?
[NAEGI gasps]
[NAEGI]
You cut off your arm?
That's one way, I guess.
[JUZO] Figured I could make
the scene before it happened.
I could meet whoever's behind
this God-forsaken
game face-to-face.
Take the Attacker
and be done with it.
[NAEGI] There is no Attacker.
There never was.
Huh?
[NAEGI]
It was suicide.
The victims, they
were all brainwashed
into killing themselves by what
they saw on the monitors.
[NAEGI]
When the time limit was up,
we were all knocked unconscious.
But whoever was closest
to a monitor got woken up
by a special signal
from their bangles.
[NAEGI] Awake and alone, they
were subjected to a video.
After that...
Who did this?
What sicko piece of shit
thinks this is entertaining?
That I don't know.
At least not yet.
But they wouldn't even have
to be here for it to work.
What are you tellin' me?
They could've set this up?
Controlled it remotely?
Probably.
On the bright side,
at least we don't have to
suspect each other anymore.
[JUZO chuckling]
What are we supposed to do now?
It's all a shell game.
We've been manipulated from
some unknown other place.
Killing each other like
a bunch of animals.
Yukizome. Gozu. Kimura.
Some video brainwashed 'em
into taking their own lives?
All the horrible things we've
done to smoke out the killer
and it's been us.
Son of a bitch!
What are you doing?
Let's end this game.
If we destroy all the monitors,
that should do it.
[JUZO]
Heh.
You got any idea how many
of those things there are?
[NAEGI]
Uh... But--
[JUZO]
Don't let me stop you.
Just don't expect me
to help either.
[JUZO] True story.
I wanted you to die.
Heh. I'd have gladly
done it myself.
See, I'm not a man who
can forgive and forget.
I hated you.
No, from the moment
you walked out
of Hope's Peak High School
alive, I loathed you.
Despised you.
So I'm not gonna lie,
when Munakata told you
to kill yourself, I thought,
"It's about damn time."
But why? I don't...
[JUZO] Because... you defeated
Junko Enoshima.
Yeah, 's right. Bitch
played me like a fiddle.
I knew she was up to something
and I kept my mouth shut.
I had one job and I botched it.
This is the result.
It's all on me.
I couldn't stop everyone dying.
I couldn't kill you
for Munakata.
And in the end,
he threw me away.
Like an old pair of boots.
[NAEGI]
He was wrong.
It's the game!
The man was fooled
into believing
you'd gone over to the enemy!
[JUZO]
No kidding.
Oh snap! Kyoko's
theory was bang-on!
I don't believe it.
Everyone really was forced
to kill themselves.
[ASAHINA]
Okay, but by who?
[MUNAKATA]
There's only one possibility.
Apart from me, there's
only one human being
capable of altering this
facility's machinery,
who knows it like
the back of his hand.
He warned me.
Told me that in a
manner of speaking
the Attacker was all of us.
I refused to believe him.
He built the Foundation
from the ground up.
In fact, he was the former
principal of Hope's Peak.
Kazuo Tengan.
[ASAHINA]
Oh, that can't be right!
[MUNAKATA] We've established
that those closest to a monitor
when the time limit ran out were
compelled to commit suicide.
Tengan's Forbidden Action
was answering a
question with a lie.
And since any of us could
potentially become the Attacker,
he told me the truth.
But... Oh my God.
Why would Chairman Tengan
want us all to kill each other?
[MUNAKATA]
Is it not perfectly obvious?
Kazuo Tengan...
...was the true
Remnant of Despair.
No way!
That can't be the answer!
He was the Foundation's
leader for God's sake!
How could--? How could
he do such a thing?
[MUNAKATA] Who knows?
But he's the only solution.
Naegi. Have I told you?
Chisa Yukizome was with
the Remnants as well.
No.
But she was my teacher.
[MUNAKATA]
I know.
She was part of an undercover
investigation into Hope's Peak
while you were there.
Everything we could find,
every shred of evidence,
every possible lead pointed
directly at Junko Enoshima.
And yet, Yukizome and Sakakura
both insisted on her innocence.
Foolishly, I took
them at their word.
[MUNAKATA]
Worst mistake of my life.
[MUNAKATA
They were my friends,
and Tengan took
advantage of that.
I didn't know.
Well damn. Guess I'm a Despair.
Huh. Wish I could
find the humor in--
[JUZO] This is what I get for
letting Enoshima off the hook.
[JUZO] Always been
too much of a softie.
'Least that's what
they'll say about me.
Okay, what's happening?
[NAEGI]
Those are the emergency lights.
Naegi, take a look!
I think the monitors
are offline.
The power's been shut off!
[NAEGI]
But by who?
[gasps]
Sakakura!
He must be in
the breaker room!
From there, he can cut off
power to the entire building!
[NAEGI]
You think he'd do that?
I don't like this, guys.
Something tells me we should've
found the breaker room first.
Munakata, please.
He's out there trying
to save you. Go to him.
He's not the enemy!
Even if you're right...
...I ran him through
and left him to die.
He was my... my friend.
Is your friend!
If he didn't believe in you,
he wouldn't be doing this!
Please! You have
to let him know!
Look around you.
The power's been cut off.
He's shutting down
the game. All for you!
I deserve what you
did to me. I get it.
And damn it all,
I want you to live!
[beeping]
The arm bangles!
Mu... na... ka... ta.
Forgive me...
Seems I'm always....
...always too late.
[AGENT E] Do we have confirmed
survivors, or don't we?
[AGENT B] If you can hear me,
try to make a noise!
[AGENT C]
A few are hangin' on!
[AGENT D] I need a
stretcher over here now!
Save the Advance Team, damn it!
Blast! What the holy
hell is going on?
So, Mitarai.
The video I saw,
it was able to
brainwash a person
into actually
killing themselves.
Think it's fair to assume
that's not something
a normal person could make?
[MITARAI]
Wait...
[NAEGI]
I mean, seriously,
I wouldn't even know
where to begin.
You're the former Super High
School-Level Animator.
Do you know anything about it?
I-I'm sorry.
But it wasn't me.
No, I wasn't accusing you--
Blame Junko Enoshima!
She used my technology!
Junko Enoshima?
[ASAHINA]
What are you talking about?
[phone ringing]
[MITARAI]
It's Tengan.