[KIZAKURA] So far so good,
all things considered.
We're the only two
left alive, aren't we?
[KIZAKURA]
Yep.
[KIZAKURA] Y'know,
I used to be teacher, right?
So this ain't exactly
my area of expertise.
No kidding? Same here.
I was a gym teacher
back in the day.
I'm not surprised.
Heh. You, uh, oughta think
about doing this for a livin'.
[AGENT A]
No thanks.
I'm more cut out for
the educator's life.
What about you?
[KIZAKURA]
Eh. I was reasonably terrible.
Loved the hell
out of it, though.
More than the kids did anyway.
[AGENT A chuckles]
[KIZAKURA]
Get down!
Hey! You all right?
[gasps]
[KIZAKURA groaning]
[KIZAKURA]
Damn it to hell.
Kyoko...
[HAGAKURE]
Son of a bitch!
'Course, the smart thing
would've been to stay hidden,
but no!
[HAGAKURE]
Uh?
[TOGAMI]
Ha!
Still alive and kicking, I see.
Togami Party! Hey!
Call me that again
and I'm leaving.
[NAEGI]
Somebody's gonna die...
....because of me.
[KOMARU]
Makoto.
Whatever's going on there,
it seems pretty awful.
But you did make a promise.
You're coming for me
when all this is over.
Sure, I mean, nobody'd ever
call you tough or anything,
but you're definitely
not the kind of guy
to go back on his word, right?
Try not to worry.
One way or another,
you're gonna get through this.
I can wait. I believe in you.
[NAEGI]
Wow, Komaru. You've changed.
You're so grown up now.
Almost like a whole new person.
[KOMARU] Um. It took
you this long to notice?
[NAEGI] Heh. I'm a
little slow sometimes.
Ugh. What a tender
sibling moment.
It's enough to gimme a migraine.
Anyway, hang in there
a little longer, 'kay?
Meantime, I'll do
whatever I can from here.
[NAEGI] Don't worry.
I'll keep that promise!
[NAEGI]
I will come for you.
[ASAHINA] You're an awesome
big brother. Just sayin'.
[NAEGI]
Oh, God. Asahina, I didn't--
[beeping]
[USAMI] Alert! Alert! Switching
to auto-remote functionality.
[ASAHINA]
What's wrong with her?
She's a robot? What the heck?
That doesn't look good.
And since this isn't a hallway,
I say we run like hell!
[NAEGI]
Right!
[ASAHINA]
C'mon!
[gasps]
[ASAHINA]
Um, Naegi?
[NAEGI]
Munakata.
[MUNAKATA]
There you are.
Filthy traitor.
[ASAHINA, NAEGI gasp]
Whoa! Heads up!
[USAMI] Standby for Future
Foundation Member analysis.
Matching to current database.
[ASAHINA, NAEGI gasp]
[USAMI] Kyosuke Munakata.
Threat level: S.
[USAMI]
Switching to....
...Berserker Mode.
So, uh, now what?
Well, while they're busy,
let's make a break for it.
'Kay.
Resistance is futile.
The Future Foundation
is destined to triumph.
I swear it.
[ASAHINA] Okay, talk to me.
Where we goin'?
[NAEGI] I'm not sure,
but Togami'll be here soon.
We have to find Kirigiri.
[ASAHINA]
You got it!
[NAEGI]
Munakata.
[MITARAI] Well? Any clue
who the Attacker might be?
[KIRIGIRI]
It's a work in progress.
I need more information.
[KIZAKURA]
Man, oh man.
Someone's been a
busy little bee.
What is all that stuff?
Traps set by our
late friend Izayoi.
Watch where you sit. Seriously.
If these bad boys are
anything to go on,
the couch's probably
rigged, too.
Rigged? For what?
To blow your ass
into next Thursday.
[MITARAI yelps]
You surprise me.
[KIZAKURA]
Hm?
You're better at this sort
of thing than I expected.
Well, thanks I guess.
Mm.
The Foundation don't
pick us at random.
'Scuse me. Shouldn't we leave?
The Attacker's bound
to come back.
He's got a point.
We hang around looking for clues
we'll all end up just like Yoi.
[KIRIGIRI]
Stop.
We'll leave when I'm done
investigating. Period.
[KIZAKURA chuckles]
[RURUKA grunts]
Did you find something?
[KIRIGIRI] Maybe.
See this scuff on the floor?
[MITARAI]
Interesting.
[clatter]
[groans] Ow.
[MITARAI]
Oh! Are you okay?
Yeah. Sure.
Really? You gotta be
careful there, doll face.
[RURUKA] Heh. I'm a bit
of a klutz sometimes.
[KIZAKURA]
Mh-hm.
Well that's a relief.
I thought you were
tryin' to monkey-wrench
the investigation
for a second.
Ha!
Says the geezer who smells
like he's had a few.
I don't have to listen
to this garbage.
No, I don't suppose you do.
Just like I don't have to
listen to the unsavory stuff
the grapevine says about you.
For example.
[RURUKA]
Uh. Yes?
[KIZAKURA] Rumor has it you and
some of the younger members
have formed your very
own splinter group
within the Foundation.
Sounds like you're in a real
bad spot with the higher ups
over the whole mess.
Which of course makes all the
talk about you wantin' to start
a new organization
much more believable.
Hey.
You're with the Vice Chairman's
faction. What've you heard?
Huh?
[RURAKA, MITARAI gasp]
So Izayoi got himself
murdered, huh?
[KIRIGIRI]
You.
[JUZO]
Welp, too bad, so sad.
'Least now there's one less
of you in Munakata's way.
Killin' four people's
easier 'n killin' five.
--[MITARAI whimpers]
--[KIZAKURA] Hm.
[HAGAKURE] Togami Party!
Yo! Toga! Toga!
[HAGAKURE]
These boxes weigh a ton, man.
You just gonna stand there
or you gonna help me?
[TOGAMI]
Lift with the knees.
And do try to be quick about it.
The Remnants of Despair might
be sending reinforcements.
[HAGAKURE] Wow.
Thanks for cuttin' me a break.
'Preciate it.
[HAGAKURE groans]
[HAGAKURE] Can't we storm
the place already?
Bet Naegi's coolin' his jets
while we're all out here
bustin' our humps.
[TOGAMI] There's no reason to
assume our friends are cozy.
[HAGAKURE]
I didn't say they were,
but at least they
got each other.
Safety in numbers!
[TOGAMI]
Hmph.
Stay alive, my old comrades.
Don't you dare die before
I can come to the rescue.
Kyoko Kirigiri.
I screwed up lettin' you
get away earlier. Not again.
Really?
Do yourself a favor.
Have the sense to stay down.
Take my word for it.
I'd love nothin' better
than to play possum.
But hell, I'm the oldest
one here by a mile.
Etiquette dictates
I'm responsible
for how we slug this out.
Speaking of which,
I can't help but notice
you feel obliged to use a knife,
Mr. Former Boxer.
I think your Forbidden
Action prohibits you
from throwing a punch!
Hit one of us and it's
curtains for ya! Maybe.
Doesn't mean I can't
eviscerate you.
[KIZAKURA] Wait, are you
saying I got it right, or--?
How 'bout I tell you
my Forbidden Action?
Why not? We'll treat it like
a trust-building exercise.
You can see it, right? Hold on,
she's coming around again.
I'm not allowed to
open my left hand.
Why bother tellin' me this?
You pullin' a fast
one or somethin'?
[KIZAKURA]
Face the facts, big stuff.
Punching is what you do best.
As far as I know, it's the
one thing you're good at.
And I'm all about whatever
levels the playing field.
Must suck for Munakata.
Without Chisa,
all he has to rely on
is a gorilla with roid-rage.
I'm startin' to think no one
actually likes the guy.
Sorry. I'm talkin' about
the Vice Chairman.
[JUZO] You are not even worthy
of speaking that man's name.
You can stand there or
do something about it.
Oh, that's right, your track
record's been a joke
where that's concerned.
Don't you dare go there!
Yeah, I dropped the ball,
but I'll be damned if I make
the same mistake twice!
I gave Munakata my vow!
[yells]
Aah. That one's on me.
I forgot it was there.
Sorry. Stupid traps.
[KIZAKURA sighs]
[KIZAKURA] Feels like today
woulda been a good time
for me to buy a lottery ticket.
Wait, so, you were
trying to lead him
to that exact spot
the whole time?
Let's say, sure.
I suggest we take this
opportunity to tie him up.
I assume you wanna
keep investigating.
Right. Back to it, then.
[chuckles]
[KIRIGIRI gasps]
[music plays]
[yells]
[growls]
[KIRIGIRI]
Kizakura, why?
[JIN] Sweetie, stop being
such a wiggle worm. Heh.
Up you go!
Hey, look at me! I'm a birdie!
[JIN]
I know!
[KIZAKURA] Come on, guys.
You want the picture or not?
Stay still.
Perfect.
[KIZAKURA]
Huh.
What do ya know...
I was a man of my word.
Jin...
[MITARAI]
This was all you, wasn't it?!
You've got something planned!
[RURUKA]
Um, yeah.
The idea is to kill all of you.
Now there's only two people
left to worry about.
This one, I need.
Aw, poor baby. Let's fix you up.
Yeah, you love a taste of the
sweet stuff, don't ya, big boy?
Of course you do.
Well? Would you like another?
I thought so.
Take care of our
friends, won't you?
Kill them both, and you can
have all the chocolate
your widdle heart desires.
Enough to last you
the rest of your life.
No! You stay away from us!
He's not listening.
His head's too filled with
thoughts of sweet, sweet candy
to give a damn
what anybody says.
Except of course the person
who'll give him his next hit.
[groaning]
[gasps]
[JUZO]
Ow.
Damn you all to hell!
You miserable,
conniving pieces of crap!
I'm no one's puppet.
Get ready to join
Izayoi and Kizakura!
Every last one of you bastards!
[KIRIGIRI]
Just a moment.
[JUZO]
Huh?
I understand why you've
been acting so bizarrely.
[JUZO]
What?
It wasn't the Attacker who
killed Sohnosuke Izayoi.
It was you.
[yelps]
Yeah?
I don't care who did what to
who, you're all gonna die.
Right here, right now,
by my hands!
You could do that.
You could also use your head.
Why resort to wholesale violence
when solving this particular
murder might actually present us
with a means of escape?
Don't you agree, Andoh?
What're you talking about?
The Attacker's the
one who killed Yoi.
[KIRIGIRI]
Wrong.
The crime scene was
carefully staged
to give us that impression.
In reality, he was killed
by his Forbidden Action.
Most traces of the poison's
effects were concealed,
but not all.
To a keen observer, his corpse
left no room for doubt.
Don't be ridiculous!
There's a knife in his chest!
[KIRIGIRI]
Put there after he died.
Originally, the knife came
from Kimura's body.
Wait, you tellin' me
Kimura's dead?
Yes. Dispatched by a solitary
stab wound to the heart.
We found her body
not far from here.
At this point, the Attacker has
claimed multiple victims,
each killed in the
exact same manner.
However, in Izayoi's case,
the MO deviated.
The stab wound wasn't
in the typical place,
and the body showed
no signs of blood loss.
In other words, our friend here
was stabbed after he died.
The killer used the knife from
Kimura's body to throw us off.
[JUZO] So the Attacker got
Kimura, but not Izayoi.
You're sure of that?
Indeed. Absolutely positive.
Okay. Then explain.
Izayoi's Forbidden
Action was eating.
If the knife wasn't
responsible, well then,
by deception or
against his will,
he was fed something and
poisoned by his bangle.
And since...
...his saliva tasted sweet,
we can deduce from this he ate
one of Andoh's confections.
You licked... saliva?
From a body?
Yes, I did.
A detective does
what's necessary.
He was shrewd.
Not a man to trifle with.
Getting him to eat
must've been difficult.
But you, a specialist
who deals in sweets,
with whom he was
exceptionally close...
How can you blame me?
Yoi was on my side!
Why would I have killed him?
The motive is clear.
[gasps]
Just as I thought.
[JUZO]
Wha--? What the--?
[MITARAI] A secret entrance?
But how did you know?
[KIRIGIRI]
The scuff marks on the floor.
And one shelf wasn't
flush with the rest.
Put those observations together,
and there's only handful
of possibilities.
[JUZO] So does this mean
we got a way outta here?
Given where it's
situated, I'd say yes.
This ought to lead to
the building's exterior.
'Course, that's assuming the
architectural plan makes sense.
Great! So you found a way out!
None of this gives me
a reason to kill him!
Under normal
circumstances, I'd agree.
But the rules of this game
compel us to do certain things
for which there'd
be no rationale
under normal circumstances.
Ruruka Andoh.
Tell us the truth.
Your Forbidden Action
is letting someone leave
the playing field, isn't it?
That's absolutely absurd.
Ah.
So when Izayoi stumbled
upon what appeared to be
an exit in this room,
his attempting to leave didn't
put you in fear of your life?
[RURUKA]
No!
You don't know anything!
He'd never betray me!
But you'd betray him.
That's it, I'm out. This stupid
game can kiss my ass.
[RURUKA]
No, stop!
If you leave, I'm a dead woman!
[JUZO] Yeah? I should
give a damn because?
[RURUKA]
Please! I'm begging you! Look...
That did the trick. Let's go.
But wait. The exit.
[RURUKA]
Wait! Wait!
[JUZO]
Let go of me! Now!
[RURUKA]
No! I don't deserve this!
Um.
Go on.
I don't understand why
Kizakura saved you.
I mean... he sacrificed
himself. For what?
[KIRIGIRI]
I have my suspicions,
but at this point,
it's all conjecture.
Wow, you really are cold.
[KIRIGIRI]
I know.
Buddy of mine hates detectives.
[KIRIGIRI]
I have to be.
I'm a detective.
[AGENT B]
Clear!
There's our way in.
[HAGAKURE]
Yeah! We did it!
[HAGAKURA laughs]
Begging your pardon.
I have to ask you
to stay out here.
[HAGAKURE]
Uh?
[AGENT B]
All right, take your...
[TOGAMI]
Ugh. The air in this place.
Reminds me of Hope's Peak.
--[AGENT B] Hey! Are you okay?
--Stop! Don't touch anything!
You idiot!
[alarm blares]
[NAEGI]
Never again.
I'm not letting them
kill anyone else!
What the--?
That felt pretty big!