[MUNAKATA]
Makoto Naegi.
[MUNAKATA] What lines are
you willing to cross
to stand on the side of Hope?
How badly do want to
see Despair vanquished?
Show us. Do the honorable
thing and commit suicide.
[MONOKUMA]
Rule Number One:
The all-important time limit.
When the clock runs out on
those nifty li'l arm bangles,
boys and girls, each
of you will be injected
with a powerful dose
of Good Night Irene.
Rule Number Two: The Attacker.
While everyone else
is catchin' dem z's,
he or she will be wide-awake
and ready to stir things up.
Once on the prowl,
the Attacker will be given
an interval good for
killing exactly one person.
Yep. 'Case you haven't figured
it out yet, there's a traitor.
And if you want the Future
Foundation to have a future,
you're gonna have ta do
somethin' about it!
Heck, why not gang up on
someone you don't like
and pray they're the Attacker?
If nap time comes and goes
and by some miracle
no one's been killed,
you win the game!
Rule Number Three:
Forbidden Actions.
Take another look
at those bangles.
Trust me on this,
you'll be glad ya did.
Note that each of you
has a specific thing
you're not allowed
to do at any time.
Performing said thing
will trigger a lethal
injection of poison
faster than you can
say "I can't even."
For example, let's pretend
I'm forbidden to laugh.
[laughing]
[music plays]
[MONOKUMA]
Aye-chi-wawa!
[MONOKUMA] So we all
clear on the rules? Good.
Oh, and uh, don't get cute
and try to rip the bangles off.
That's another surefire way
of gettin' yourself poisoned.
Have fun!
Mind those Forbidden Actions
and suss out the Attacker
before you all die one by one!
Wh-What is he
even talking about?
[MONOKUMA]
Silly me.
Something else I
forgot to mention.
The festivities are being
recorded for broadcast
to an adoring public
the world over.
That's right. You meat-bags
are a hot-ticket item.
Oh. Beg your pardon,
did I say meat-bags?
I meant survivors. Brilliant
and talented survivors.
So it's exactly like last time.
[beeping]
[USAMI yells]
[USAMI] I demand to know who's
pulling your strings, puppet!
Who the heck is that?
[KIRIGIRI]
You don't know?
She's one of the top developers
for the New World program.
[ASAHINA] Wait. You mean
that's Miss Gekkogahara?
The girl so painfully shy
she only ever talks to people
through her avatar?
Uh, ma'am? I really wouldn't...
[USAMI] I will not sit back and
allow the Future Foundation
to be hacked by
the likes of you!
[MONOKUMA]
Hm? Somebody talkin'?
Don't believe I've
had the pleasure.
Oh, honey. We gotta do
somethin' about that getup.
Ta-dah!
[USAMI]
What's going on?
My protocols are
being overridden!
How is this possible?
[MONOKUMA]
Can it, cutie pie!
Stop whining and
do as big brother says!
[USAMI] Are you trying to
suggest we're related?
[sighs]
[MONOKUMA] There we are!
Now you've got style!
[USAMI]
I-I look awful!
[MONOKUMA]
Right.
So try not to embarrass
the Future Foundation,
and best o' luck!
I'll be keepin' an eye
on ya the whole time.
[MONOKUMA laughs]
[MONOKUMA]
Buh-bye now!
Screw you! Damn son of a--
[beeping]
[USAMI] C-Can s-s-someone turn
me back to how I was, please?
[GOZU]
Who's behind this?
'S like a banquet
for a small fry.
[SEIKO] The Remnants of
Despair will pay for this.
Mark my words.
Dear oh dear. Well this
is a fine mess we're in.
Ahh!
Stop. Maybe later.
Hey, look. This is
Monokuma's MO.
He wants to tear us apart.
We have to work together.
I couldn't agree more.
[MUNAKATA] The Future
Foundation will persevere.
We will face the enemy as one.
Undivided.
[USAMI]
Oh no.
Why her?
Ugh. Out of everyone here,
why did she have to die?
[USAMI] I can't connect
to the internet now!
And my cell phone's
completely useless!
I might be able to
get us back online,
but it's gonna take a while!
Wow. You'd think we'd
have a better firewall here.
No offense, I'm just sayin'.
[USAMI]
For your information,
we are more than prepared
for an attack from outside!
I never dreamed we'd need to be
on guard against an inside job!
[ASAHINA]
An inside job?
So it's true.
One of us standing in this room
right now really is a traitor.
[USAMI] There's no other
viable explanation.
[BANDAI] Best I can tell,
nobody's stalking the hallways.
All the elevators and
windows have been sealed.
[TENGAN]
Just as I thought.
There's no escaping.
[JUZO]
That settles it.
We have to find out who the
Attacker is and kill them.
Wait! There's no
need to kill anyone.
Once we've learned
their identity,
we can just
restrain them, right?
Gamblin' with your Super High
School-Level Luck there,
big shot?
You'd just slip out of the ropes
while we were all sleepin'.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Yes, well, apart from Naegi.
The idea of confining
any of us to this room
would seem meaningless.
[JUZO]
C'mon,'fess up already!
You're with the
Remnants of Despair.
This has your stink all over it.
Calm down for a sec!
Please, You've gotta
listen to me!
And why would I do that?
Sorry, you're not gonna weasel
your way outta this one.
I'm not as easy to manipulate
as Junko Enoshima.
[ASAHINA gasps]
If you're implying what I think
you are, you're an idiot!
What?!
The strawberry seed only
shows its face three times!
Whatever you're about
to do, please don't.
I second that. Violence
is never the answer.
Plus, she's a girl.
Hate to break it to you, Gandhi.
But when you're knee-deep in
a war zone, it's anything goes!
--[music plays]
--[BANDAI groans]
Man the hell up.
This ain't the place
for diplomacy.
If we could get by on
feel-good platitudes,
we'd be outta here by now!
[SEIKO]
Move!
[SEIKO] It's too late.
I couldn't save him.
Ew. What just happened?
Was he attacked?
Not attacked.
[KIRIGIRI]
It was this.
[KIRIGIRI] "Witnessing
violence by participants."
[GOZU]
Juzo, what have you done?
Oh, I get it.
That's gonna be how
they pick us off.
[USAMI]
E-Everyone, keep your heads!
We have the means to prevent
this from happening again.
First, we need to
consult the bangles
and confirm our specific
Forbidden Actions!
If you think I'll share my
Achilles Heel with you people,
you're sorely mistaken!
Some of us clearly
can't be trusted!
Fair point.
That of course,
and for all we know,
revealing our Forbidden
Action may just be
someone's Forbidden Action.
[GOZU]
Yes. But even so--
[MUNAKATA] We need to decide
on a course of action.
Evidently there's no
means of putting a stop
to the game itself.
So we'll find the attacker.
No doubt each of us has
already picked out a favorite.
And since time is short,
I say we put it to a vote.
Everyone, point to the person
you believe to be responsible.
[USAMI] What? W-W-Why
would you suspect me?!
Meh. Call it a hunch.
[ASAHINA gasps]
Whoa! Now hold on a second!
It's decided. Makoto Naegi.
What lines are you
willing to cross
to stand on the side of Hope?
How badly do want to
see Despair vanquished?
Show us.
Do the honorable thing
and commit suicide.
[ASAHINA] You expect Naegi to
kill himself? Just like that?
This is insane!
There's not enough evidence
to point the finger at anyone!
I assume you have
an alternative.
Or should we be content to wait
for the Attacker's next move?
[ASAHINA]
Well, no, but--
Be fair! What if he's
not the one responsible?
Then we keep voting. Sooner
or later we'll get it right.
A desperate measure, perhaps,
but effective nonetheless.
Good for weeding out traitors.
[TENGAN]
Munakata, you can't be serious!
Oh, I'm quite serious, sir.
The Remnants of Despair must
be eliminated at any cost.
Naegi understands that.
Better than most, I'd wager.
When our backs are against the
wall, cooperation is essential.
You agree, don't you?
Or maybe you're torn.
[NAEGI]
You're asking me to--
[JUZO]
If you won't, then I will!
[GOZU]
That's enough!
[GOZU] Hope won't come in
the form of a comrade's death!
[MUNAKATA]
A noble sentiment.
But you seem to have
conveniently forgotten
countless comrades
have already fallen
at the hands of the enemy.
Unless we want their sacrifice
to be meaningless,
we have to fight fire with fire.
Let's go.
Do not get in our way!
[growls]
Guess someone's
itchin' for a fight!
C'mon! We gotta
get out of here!
Wait. They'll rip
each other apart.
[ASAHINA] If that's what they
wanna do, more power to 'em!
They're not gonna
listen to reason!
Right now, we run!
Uh, it's not that simple.
Believe me, I would if I could.
But under the circumstances.
What?
Normally this would be the
other way around, but whatever!
[NAEGI]
Asahina!
[KIRIGIRI]
Naegi. Be safe.
[footsteps]
Violence is not the answer.
The only thing it
creates is Despair.
Uh, excuse me, Chairman,
what are you doing?
Isn't this harassment?
Not remotely.
My intentions are pure.
Please. You're safe.
Ugh. Look at it.
They used explosives to
block off the entrances.
Step carefully. Floor's bound
to be weak in spots.
[explosion]
--[NAEGI] What was that?
--Naegi!
[MUNAKATA]
There you are.
[GOZU] That does it!
You've gone too far, asshole!
I will not stoop
to killing allies!
Period. End of story.
I'd sooner lay down my life.
The Great Gozu knows
the cost of doing right,
and he's willing to pay it!
[MUNAKATA] That's how you
combat Despair? Pathetic.
[GOZU]
What did you say to m--?
Why can't you understand?
If just one of their
number is left alive,
the Despairs crawl
back like roaches!
Every single member must be
eradicated once and for all.
Collateral damage is
inevitable of course.
But such is my duty.
I swore an oath!
That, my friend,
is the true cost of Hope.
[tires screeching]
[USAMI] Th-There they are!
Our 12 o'clock!
Miss Gekkogahara?
Huh?!
You're kidding me!
It does this now?
[GOZU]
Not a bad throw.
[yells]
[ASAHINA screams]
[GOZU]
He's not following us.
Guess not.
[GOZU] Not now. But you can
be sure he's got a plan.
For the moment, I suggest we
get as far away as possible.
Uh, guys, we're almost
at the time limit.
[GOZU]
Right, then.
Let's hide somewhere the
Attacker wouldn't think to look.
[USAMI]
Wait up! I'm coming with you!
It's too scary out here all
by myself. Pretty please?
You are just adorable--
Oh. My bad.
So I guess we're
dealing with a traitor.
Please tell me I'm not the only
one who's positive it's Kimura.
Seems kinda obvious. Smart.
Y' betray your friends once,
the second time's easy.
I know, she and Hope's Peak are
the same as the Foundation.
Makes me sick.
Some people are just
rotten to the core.
You okay?
Why's this happening
to us, Naegi?
It's just like last time.
They're just-- They're gonna
make us do it all again.
Murder each other
till we trust no one.
[NAEGI]
It's not like last time.
What are you talking about?
Of course it is.
[NAEGI]
I'm here.
[gasps]
And not just me.
Don't forget Kirigiri.
We're friends now.
Last time, we didn't
even know each other.
This time, different ballgame.
We have an idea
of what to expect.
And we know that
we're not alone.
We do. Absolutely!
We're a team right off the
bat now. That's a big plus.
What'd I tell ya?
Not so bad when you
put it into perspective.
[GOZU chuckles]
[GOZU]
Oh, Naegi.
You're exactly the man portrayed
in the Hope's Peak broadcast.
Incredible.
During School Life
of Mutual Killing,
you never gave in to Despair.
Countless lives were
changed because of that.
We need you. Hope is the
engine that drives our future.
Uh, that's kind of you to
say, but a little overdone.
[GOZU] The Chairman was
thrilled to have you.
Said with you on board,
a new era was dawning.
The Future Foundation
would be revolutionized!
So spare me your
slump-shouldered modesty.
People are rooting
for you, jackass!
[NAEGI]
Yes, sir.
[MUNAKATA] I take it you
didn't find the others?
What can I say? They
split up and ran. Cowards.
Here we are at the
threshold of Hell
and all anyone gives a damn
about is saving themselves.
So I assume you gotta plan?
The same one as always.
We annihilate the Despairs.
[JUZO]
Then I s'pose I'll protect you.
Nothin' new 'bout that.
[JUZO]
I know what Hope looks like.
As long as you
make it outta this,
the Future Foundation
can rebuild.
Them's the breaks.
Anyone I don't trust
is gonna wind up dead.
And I'll be damned if Yukizome's
murder goes un-avenged.
[USAMI] Get ready.
Time is almost up.
[GOZU] Good luck, comrades.
Nothing left but to pray.
Naegi, what do we do?
I'm scared.
Something tells me this
will only get worse.
We're gonna be okay.
Super High
School-Level Luck here!
Nothin' to worry about!
'S long as we stick close,
it'll rub off on ya!
It isn't fair.
Look at you. I mean, how do
you always stay so positive?
[music plays]
I appreciate it, Naegi.
Like I even did anything.
Give yourself some credit. Asa--
[MONOKUMA]
Wakey-wakey, Attacker.
The killin' clock is tickin'!
Time for the hunt!
Get out there and
make some magic!
That's it. Low-hangin'
fruit for the pickin'!
Who's the lucky target today?
[gasps]