[MONAKA] The Junko Enoshima
you worshipped is no more!
And why?
Because of that poopie-head,
Makoto Naegi!
[MONAKA crying]
[MONAKA]
Despair lost.
Hope mopped the floor
with our collective butts.
How sad is that? Like,
really, really, really sad!
The worst thing ever!
You don't even know!
[wailing]
[MONAKA] Shut up!
You're next on the hit list!
Hope has its sights trained
and its finger on the trigger!
But take heart,
my beloved Monokumas,
it ain't over till
the fat lady screams!
Oh, yes! Your Monaka
is still here!
And as the heir of big sis
Junko's Despair factor,
I shall continue her legacy!
Because a world brimming with
hope is unbelievably drab.
Oh, God.
People must come to know the joy
of raw, unmitigated Despair.
I, Junko Enoshima the 2nd,
aka Monaka Towa,
will stem the tide!
Just you wait!
The Future Foundation,
all humanity will drown
in a sea of desolation!
[NAGISA]
Yes, that's right.
She's commandeered a building
on the outskirts of town.
Kind of a lair. Careful.
Apparently the place is guarded
by an army of Monokumas.
I hate to say it,
but our hands are tied.
We don't have the manpower.
Unfortunately, getting
in there is up to you.
My apologies.
Stay sharp.
Monaka Towa is setting herself
up to be the next Junko.
And she's every bit as
intelligent as Enoshima.
If she's still trying
to plan something,
whatever it is, shut her down.
Just... promise me you'll try
not to be so hard on the girl.
She's a friend.
At least, she used to be.
[KOMARU]
I know, Shingetsu. Sorry.
Gang way! Comin' through!
[FUKAWA panting]
Will you slow down for a second?
I'm a book nerd!
Running isn't my thing! Ugh!
[KOMARU]
My name is Komaru Naegi.
Hope is not my thing.
Neither is Despair.
I'm just a normal high school
girl, like you'd find anywhere.
[KOMARU]
Fire in the hole!
[KOMARU] When the Biggest,
Most Atrocious,
Despair-Inducing Incident
in Human History struck,
I survived.
But got separated
from my family.
[KOMARU]
Suck on this!
Link!
[KOMARU]
Now here I am, in Towa City,
neutralizing demonic teddy
bears with my friend, Touko.
Please. Can't we rest?
[chuckles]
[laughing]
Don't let the pearly whites
fool ya. I'm a psycho killer!
Heh.
Komaru, honey,
lay off the carbs.
You're startin' to look like
one of these tubby li'l terrors.
That's mean!
My weight is perfectly below
average, thank you! Hmph!
[KOMURA]
This town,
it's like playing expert
level without cheat codes.
[KOMURA]
Paralyze!
No choice but to keep going.
While I wait for my brother
to end this stupid war
between Hope and Despair.
Look it up online!
Let go! We're not done yet!
Ugh, what the hell
is wrong with you?
Running blind into
an enemy swarm's
a good way to get dead!
Unless o'course,
you like it rough. Heh.
[KOMARU]
No! Knock it off!
Ugh.
Look, I know you're worried
about Makoto, and that's okay,
but play it cool,
or you're gonna end up
a pile of mincemeat.
Yeah. I know.
Well, not that I
really give a damn.
If you got a death
wish it's-- A-choo!
What?
Fine. Break's over.
Let's get on with it.
But I haven't even
caught my breath yet!
[KOMARU] Holy crap.
That is a lot of Monokumas.
This is one time I wish Togami's
intel wasn't so accurate.
I-I don't dare botch this
mission, you understand me?
If I'm lucky, Master
Byakuya asks for my help
maybe once in a blue moon.
I can't fail. I won't.
No! Ohh! My sweet prince!
[TOGAMI]
Fukawa, my darling.
A poet would be hard-pressed
to describe your beauty.
Oh, stop it.
You are obviously far
more beautiful than me.
Far more handsome!
Perhaps I'm lost in
your eyes, perhaps not.
Perhaps I should put
you in handcuffs.
Please, Master, take me skiing.
I want us to cause an
avalanche with our love.
[CHILDREN]
Papa! Mummsie!
[TOGAMI]
Oh! What do we have here?
Are you behaving,
my little cherubs?
[CHILDREN]
Yes, sir!
Um, my dear.
Whom might I ask is that
extraordinarily homely
and vulgar young woman
blending into the background?
Oh. Pay her no mind.
It's just my lady-in-waiting,
Chibi Komaru.
Isn't she precious?
Hi. I'm Chibi Komaru.
[TOGAMI]
Fascinating.
I don't believe I've
ever met someone
whose plainness so
utterly defies explanation.
You're gonna make me blush.
You're simply ravishing
by comparison!
Stop! No, go on.
Come, let us throw
propriety to the wind
and conceive our 19th child
right here, my mountain orchid.
Darling. Please,
the others will see us.
Oh my goodness,
this is happening!
[TOGAMI]
I don't care. Say yes!
I'll go lay out fresh clothes
for Madam. Don't mind me, guys.
[AGENT A]
Everything all right, sir?
You seem uncomfortable?
Yes.
I was just struck by
the uncanny sense
that a certain someone
is fantasizing
well beyond the scope
of her station.
I'm fine. Continue the report.
Sir.
In accordance with
our earlier findings,
none of the other branches are
registering Remnant activity.
Nor is the situation in the
facility being broadcast.
If the Remnants
of Despair intend
for Foundation brass to kill one
another, as Naegi maintains,
broadcasting it would
be an essential part
of their broader objective.
And yet, so far,
no other divisions report
the slightest indication
of Remnant activity.
This new Killing Game
has to be a means
to a far more nefarious end.
What the devil are
they playing at?
Attention, all agents.
As I speak, the leaders
of the Future Foundation
are under a clear
and present threat.
There is no time to waste.
Let's show the enemy
what we're capable of.
Do not fret.
As long as I draw breath,
this organization will not fall.
This I swear by the dignity
of the Togami name.
[KOMARU] Something tells me
this might be her hideout.
Way to be subtle about it, huh?
I thought the brat was supposed
to be hyper intelligent.
But I'm starting to think
she's an imbecile.
I mean, seriously.
Who does that?
[KOMARU]
Right?
'Kay. Well, we're here so...
I cannot fail.
Here goes nothing!
Let's take the slut
down in record time
so I can get back to bumpin'
uglies with Master Sweetcheeks!
Mr. Stork, you're about to put
in some serious overtime!
[laughing]
[MONAKA laughing]
[MONAKA]
Oh my God, finally.
Ew! Nobody needs to
see your friendship
hanging out all over the place!
We get it. Together you
can brave anything.
Blah, blah, blah.
You're just pooling
your lunch money
to buy last week's
lottery ticket.
Why doesn't anyone understand
how wonderful Despair is?
Are they that blind?
Ugh. It really breaks
my heart, you know?
Like, I'm in tears right now.
[MONAKA cries]
[MONAKA}
It's not fair.
Maybe Despair's not trendy
with Junko out of the picture.
Maybe-- Maybe
Monoka isn't trendy!
Maybe the world doesn't
want me anymore!
Oh, well!
Meh. It's not like I can't blow
this popsicle stand, right?
Time for me to leave
the world, or destroy it.
Yep! Those are my options!
And the best part?
It's not a difficult choice.
[MONAKA giggling]
I don't even know
how we did that.
I haven't taken out that
many Monokuma's in forever.
I just need a minute here.
Ugh, my breath!
[KOMARU]
Yeah, it stinks.
No, you jerk,
I need to catch it!
[KOMARU]
Uh-huh.
Definitely looks like she's
got something in the works.
[FUKAWA]
Stupid little brat.
She's been so quiet lately I
thought we were done with her.
What on earth is she up to now?
[BOTH gasp]
[MONAKA] Hello there, girls!
Welcome to the party!
I'm so glad you made it.
And I sure ain't kitten!
Wh-What are you trying to do?
[chuckles]
Do you think you're dumb?
Consider yourself
painfully average?
Having trouble
deciding what side
of the Hope/Despair
fence you're on?
Well, honey, put all
the mess behind you!
Monaka Towa is here to take Hope
completely and utterly
out of the equation!
Impossible! You're insane!
So you're behind what's going
on at Foundation Headquarters?
I, the great Monaka Towa,
true heir to Junko
Enoshima's legacy,
am the only one who could
ever hope to bring Naegi
to the deplorable depths
of deadly Despair!
Ah. Of course.
I thought that hairstyle
looked oddly familiar.
I owe the man a debt.
Because of him, I'm more Junko
Enoshima than the original!
Can you believe it?
She'd be so proud!
You're not gonna lay
a hand on my brother!
[laughs]
Sorry, sweetheart.
Home field advantage!
[FUKAWA]
Look out!
There's even more
here than outside.
Oh, God. Just fight
for as long as you can.
Fine. I surrender.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[MONAKA] Did I stutter?
I said I surrender.
Lemme make sure
I get this straight.
You're backing down? That's it?
Yup. If we rumble, it's a
forgone conclusion I'd lose.
Hope is just way too
stubborn to die.
Despair can win the battle,
but never the war.
[sighs]
[MONAKA] Don't you see?
I was hoping to defeat you.
Irony.
I'm done. Monoka out.
[BOTH gasp]
Uh... What the hell is this?
Ugh. My room. What's it
look like? Come on.
[FUKAWA]
Good lord, it's a pigsty!
Damn! And if you're sayin'
that, you know it's bad.
Ha-ha. You're hilarious.
So, uh, what happens now?
I thought you were all about
your wannabe-big sister's legacy
and becoming the Super High
School-Level Despair.
[MONAKA]
Yeah, no.
That was this whole phase I was
going though. I'm over it now.
Let's pretend it never happened.
Well that's good.
But we're still gonna
need some information.
[MONAKA]
Ugh. I don't know anything.
Whoever's behind the Mutual
Killing Game, it's not me.
That tactic is so
cliché nowadays.
Frankly I've got better
things to do with my time.
Huh?
But if you're not the
mastermind, what are you doing?
[MONAKA] Um, I suppose
you can call me a lurker.
Is that a thing?
Sadly, yes. She's just
been watching.
[MONAKA] I wanted to see this
Makoto Naegi guy up close,
that's all.
I might've had a little fun with
ketchup for old time's sake.
Heh. Nothing major.
Nothing major?
You murdered Gekkogahara
for crying out loud!
[MONAKA]
Oh, yeah.
Well, apart from that,
nothing major.
Um. What made you this way?
You had to have been
normal once. You're a kid.
How'd you get to be such a lousy
excuse for a human being?
[MONAKA]
There was this person.
Kinda turned me into
an adult way too soon.
[KOMARU]
Wait.
[FUKAWA]
What?
[MONAKA] I used to listen
to him go on and on
about Hope and Despair
and yadda, yadda, yadda.
Not someone I really
wanna end up like.
[FUKAWA, KOMARU]
Uh...
[MONAKA]
So I'm done.
Total indifference is
Monoka's thing now.
Then who's behind this?
Tell us who's attacking
my brother and the others!
Sorry. No idea.
'Course there is one
thing I could tell you.
[chuckles]
Makoto Naegi is in for
the shock of his life.
And he doesn't even know
that because of him,
one of the survivors
from big sis' game
is gonna bite the big one!
[gasps]
Uh?
[MONAKA] Monaka knows who,
but she's too lazy to say.
Guess I'm just a lousy
excuse for a human being.
What? No, please!
You have to tell us!
[MONAKA]
Leave me alone. Google it. Jeez.
[KOMARU]
Don't make me hurt you!
Oh, I see how it is.
You want us to believe
you're indifferent,
but you're still on
the side of Despair.
[MONAKA] E for effort,
but I'm not biting.
[SHO] You have the rest of
your life to 'fess up, bitch!
I'm the sort of gal who
reads mystery novels
by skipping to the end!
[MONAKA] You're really worried
about Naegi, aren't you?
[SHO]
Hell, no!
I just don't like loose
ends! Now spill it!
[MONAKA] Ugh. You didn't
hear it from me, okay?
The victim will be--
Agh! That does it!
She dies now!
[KOMARU]
No, stop! You can't!
Let go of me, DeKomaru!
We promised not to go too
hard on her! Remember?
[BOTH gasp]
[MONAKA] It's been fun, ladies,
but this is goodbye.
Best of luck!
You're... leaving?
I'm setting a course
for the Final Frontier.
Outer Space! Where I'm
never leaving my room! He!
You-You've gotta be kidding!
Tramp! We're not done!
You ain't goin' nowhere!
[KOMARU]
Wait! What're you doing?
Tell me! Which of us from
the old gang's gonna die?
[KOMARU]
Touko!
Forget it! She won't talk!
If we don't get down now,
we won't be able to!
'S okay. Don't worry about me.
Just get outta here!
[KOMARU]
Screw that!
We're in this together!
I'm not leaving you!
Let's go. We need
to jump now! C'mon.
You wanna see Togami
again, don't you?
That's a low blow.
Touko, please!
[MONAKA]
Hope. Despair.
You'd think with
only two options
it'd be a fairly
straightforward choice, right?
Too complicated!
Monoka is shutting her brain
off permanently! Woohoo!
No more thinking!
There!
Heads up, we're comin' in hot!
[KOMARU]
You all right? Talk to me.
[FUKAWA groans]
[FUKAWA] Do I even wanna
know what's going on,
or was that the world
somersaulting?
Ugh. I'm gonna puke.
Uh? What? What's with that look?
Sorry, I'm just...
I'm just so--
What would I have done if
something happened to you?
[FUKAWA]
Uh.
Hey, thanks for talking
me down. I needed that.
[KOMARU]
Sure.
Unbelievable.
You think she's really
going into space?
[FUKAWA]
Who knows...
Anything's possible.
Shame someone with her
IQ chooses to waste away
in her room though.
I have a feeling
she'll change her mind
once she's grown up a little.
All she needs, really.
Give her a little time to mature
and she'll be back before long.
[FUKAWA]
Well, as far as I'm concerned,
she can stay up there.
So now what?
Kinda strange for
Togami to be late, isn't it?
[whirring]
Miss Gekkogahara?
Are you feeling okay?
[USAMI]
Big brother!
Huh?
[USAMI]
Makoto? Come in! Are you there?
Listen to me very carefully.
The person in front of
you right now isn't real.
Quite a twist, huh?
What is going on?
Hold on a minute,
you never said Gekkogahara
was your little sister!
What? No!
She's not. I-I don't--
[FUKAWA]
I think we're patched in.
Okay. I'll get in touch
with Master Byakuya.
You talk to your brother.
Tell him what she said.
Right.
Nice, we got video.
Hey, big brother!
Can you see me?
Hey, Komaru! Lookin'
good there, sis! Ha!
Wait a second. Why are you
inside...? What's going on?
So, yeah, um--
We just got some pretty
bad news actually.
Listen to me.
Monaka's not behind this,
but she did tell us someone's
gonna die 'cause of you!
Brace yourself.
She said it'll be somebody
from the first game.
One of the survivors from
Hope's Peak High School
won't make it out
of there alive.
But how could she know that?
It just doesn't make
any sense at all!
[KOMARU] I wish I knew
more, I really do.
All I can say is Monoka told us
like it was something
she knew for a fact.
I-I'm sorry. It might
be a trick, but still!
[TOGAMI]
Nonsense!
That's the most preposterous
thing I've ever heard!
One of us killed? Absurd!
Hagakure, Togami, and
Fukawa are all outside,
so it's a safe bet she wasn't
talking about one of them.
Somebody's gonna die...
...because of me.
[thud]
What?