[sighs]
[HAGAKURE] Alrighty then,
what's the plan now?
Duh! Of course.
I'm a fortune teller!
[chanting]
[HAGAKURE]
Ka!
[ALL laughing]
[HAGAKURE]
There it is!
Aw, yeah! We all live
happily ever after!
My predictions never fail!
[laughing]
I mean, sure, there's a
margin of error, but--
I'm always 30% accurate! Heh!
What's the problem?
Saying goodbye that tough?
Heh. You're not the
least bit sad to go?
Graduating makes me feel lonely.
[JUZO]
That's a weird way to see it.
'S not like we're
breakin' up the band.
[MUNAKATA]
The future belongs to us.
With our skills, the world
is our virtual oyster.
[chuckles]
I'm already the World Champ.
But hangin' with you
guys is way more fun.
Yeah, Munakata.
While it's great you have
such a laser-honed vision
of the future,
someone still has to play
your devil's advocate.
I agree.
Hope's Peak needs an
overhaul in management.
Now, while its reputation
needs a bit of mending,
there is still a
great deal of respect
for the school's
core philosophy.
And that won't change.
I'll be establishing
an overseas campus.
When it inevitably succeeds,
I'll take the helm
of the whole school.
Sakakura, after
I've seized power,
you'll be in charge of Security.
Oh, hell yeah!
Compared to winnin' this baby
here, that'd be a cakewalk.
Yukizome, I have a role
for you to play as well:
Forging relations.
Okay.
This will be how we make a
real difference in the world.
Easy, pal, 's quite a dream.
A dream? No, reality.
With you two by my side,
I'm sure of it.
I have a vision.
Together, we have a plan.
Farewell... Chisa.
[gasps]
Oh, God. Oh, God!
Kirigiri.
Kirigiri, wake up!
There is no one
to blame but you.
Makoto Naegi.
What lines are you
willing to cross
to stand on the side of Hope?
How badly do you want to
see Despair vanquished?
Coward. Why did you turn?
That's not what happened.
I only-- I only wanted to help!
Hope cannot be built
on platitudes.
They're not just platitudes!
So terribly naïve.
Did you think this could be
resolved without bloodshed?
Without lives being lost?
Yes, I did! There's no
reason she had to--!
This is not game.
There are no rules for
you to set a course by.
Hollow words are only good
for rallying the rabble
to a lost cause!
That's the nature of reality.
[yells]
Naegi! You okay? What is it?
It was just a dream.
Well, that's a relief!
Oh, man! Must've been one
heck of a dream, though!
Scared me there for a sec.
[USAMI] Me, too! The way
you were thrashing around.
Is, uh... Is everybody safe?
[ASAHINA]
You bet'cha!
We got Super High School-Level
Good Luck on our side!
Um. Something wrong?
I'm glad the three
of us are okay.
But while we were all asleep,
the Attacker must've
gotten someone.
[USAMI, ASAHINA]
Uh?
Third time. Looks like
we're all still intact.
[KIZAKURA yawning]
[KIZAKURA]
Hm?
Oh, hey. You're not
dead. Good on ya.
Uh. Guess not. Thanks.
Is-Is that, um--?
Gozu, yes. The Attacker's
second victim, poor devil.
What a way to go.
Well, what do we do now?
Drink to our continued survival?
Huh?
There's likely a third
victim waiting to be found.
I suggest we go look.
Oh, yeah. Sounds great.
[KIZAKURA]
So why're we doin' this?
To out the Attacker?
Mind you, I'm not
questioning your methods.
How many bodies you need
to figure it out, though?
You know what's funny?
I read once detectives
are why murderers exist.
Makes sense in a
warped kinda way.
Barring crimes of passion,
you gotta figure most are in it
to one-up some know-it-all.
Oo. Ha, ha. Eh...
What're you trying to say?
Don't listen to me. I'm kiddin'.
Look, a buddy of mine
hates detectives,
like seriously hates 'em.
Probably rubbed off on me.
You have a buddy?
Nobody special.
Not exactly germane
to the story, 'kay?
Humble advice from
a former teacher?
It'd do you good to break outta
that logical mindset
now and again.
I realize the world of human
emotion can get murky,
but still.
[KIRIGIRI exhales]
There you go.
Didn't that feel good?
Sure. Are you following me?
Uh. Do what?
So now I'm following you
if I happen to be walkin'
in the same direction?
[KIRIGIRI] Fine. Then I'll
go this way, thank you.
[screams]
[KIRIGIRI] A single knife
wound to the chest.
I'm assuming the
Attacker did this.
[KIZAKURA]
Hey!
Well that doesn't look healthy.
[MITARAI]
W-We found the latest victim.
[KIZAKURA]
Huh. I wouldn't be so sure.
Could you maybe...
...come with me for
just a sec, please?
Whatever it is,
we don't have time.
[KIZAKURA sighs]
Uh, yeah.
The clock's not really
on anyone's side here.
This young lady also has a
single knife wound to the chest.
Seems to be the
Attacker's preferred MO.
[MITARAI]
U-Uh, I thought only one person
was supposed to be
killed at a time.
This doesn't make any sense!
We're all members of
the Future Foundation.
Damn shame.
Well, blame the traitor.
Somebody clearly identifies
more with the Remnants.
So spill the beans. You got
yourself a favorite suspect yet?
[door opens]
[RURUKA]
Please, you gotta help me!
I'm begging you!
[NAEGI]
There.
This how we're s'posed to do it?
[USAMI]
Perfect! Well done!
One moment while I peruse the
surveillance camera network.
Yoo-hoo, latest victim,
where are you?
Whoa!
[NAEGI]
Stop!
Chairman Tengan...
[NAEGI]
It-It can't be.
[USAMI]
This wasn't the Attacker.
Tengan's wounds indicate
the use of a katana.
Munakata must've finally killed
him. I'm so terribly sorry.
Naegi?
[NAEGI] I thought if we just
talked it out, we could...
...we could come to
an understanding,
without people dying.
[NAEGI]
I really did.
[giggles]
My goodness!
So delectably sweet!
Look at the poor babies.
D'aaww, punkin'.
We need a li'l cheering up, huh?
[NAEGI]
Everything I did...
...there was no point
to any of it.
Hey, c'mon.
[USAMI]
That's not true and you know it!
It's in your nickname
for cryin' out loud!
You of all people know how
infectious hope can be!
Watching you try your very best,
my whole outlook on the
situation has changed!
And as someone who's benefited
from your unflappable attitude,
now it's my turn to give back
a smidge of that same Hope!
I'll be the first one to admit
things aren't going
so well right now.
But so what? It'll get
better before the end.
I've never been so sure of
anything in my entire life!
Me, neither. Everything's
gonna turn out for the best.
[USAMI] Wait. Take a
closer look at the body.
[ASAHINA] "I entrust the Hope
of the world to you."
Whoa. He had to
mean Naegi, right?
That couldn't have
been addressed to me.
Why not?
It's a heavy burden, sure,
but you don't have
to carry it alone.
[USAMI]
I can help, too, you know!
That's what being soul
mates is all about!
You're absolutely right.
I just have to stop
thinking like a lone wolf.
When I fought Junko Enoshima,
it certainly wasn't
a one-man show.
Heh. I-I have to remember
I'm not in this alone.
Of course not.
We'll pull through together.
As a team.
Okie dokie.
Sounds like he wants the girls
to solve his problems for him.
Frickin' loser.
Ha!
If something that cheesy
an put him back on his feet,
his head must be,
like, totally empty.
To think a whiney li'l tool like
this got the drop on Junko!
Way to set an example, big sis!
[ASAHINA]
All right, thinking caps on.
How do we beat whoever
it is at their own game?
[USAMI] Ideally, we'd find
and put a stop to the Attacker
before he or she strikes again.
Precisely how, I'm not sure.
That's an easy one!
Punch their friggin'
lights out! Yeah!
Oh, right,
our Forbidden Actions.
I hate this game so much.
Wait. What did you just say?
[ASAHINA] Oh, um.
I said I hate this game.
I mean, the rules make it
impossible to win.
It's totally rigged.
[NAEGI]
The rules... of the game.
Yet for all that heroism,
you only won because it
was no more than a game.
Out here, things
aren't so cut and dry.
In the real world,
there are no rules.
Guys, that's it!
Why are we playing Monokuma's
game in the first place?
It's so simple! We just
need to shut it down!
What're you talking about?
Any of us are free to leave
whenever we feel like it!
Uh, yeah, but correct
me if I'm wrong;
I thought we confirmed
all the exits were sealed.
Who cares when we can
just make our own exit?!
We can do it. This isn't
like the last time.
The rules don't say anything
about busting our way out.
A-ha!
There's got to be something
we can use lying around.
All we have to do is
get through the walls!
[USAMI] Or perhaps we
could have someone else
break them down from outside.
[NAEGI]
From outside?
[USAMI]
Heave-ho!
We'll use the Monitoring Room!
I'll hack into the comm network
and get us in touch with our
Future Foundation comrades
on the mainland!
They'll have the
resources to help!
[NAEGI]
That's genius!
See what happens when you
think outside the box?
Yeah, we were so caught up
trying to abide by the rules,
it didn't occur to us
to look for loopholes.
Nice work, Miss Gekkogahara!
You're a warrior of Hope!
Thought the jig was up.
Whew. Man.
[USAMI]
Oh, yeah! Darn tootin' I am!
What are we waitin' for?
Let's call for help!
[USAMI]
One moment, please,
while I calculate the
most efficient route!
Right. Let's go!
[RURUKA crying]
[RURUKA]
I can't believe Yoi's dead.
You don't understand. What'll
I do on my own? I'm helpless!
I'm sorry.
[RURUKA crying]
Please, oh please, tell me
you're not the ones behind this!
Are you the Attacker?
Am I gonna die?
No! Of course not.
[RURUKA sighs]
I believe you. Look, can
I be a part of your group?
I really can't do anything
on my own. So, you know--
I, uh--
You heard the girl.
[MITARAI] It's not as though
we can just leave her here.
Then we don't have a choice.
Thank you.
Of course.
Can we maybe go to
a different room now?
I'm sorry. I can't bear to
see him like this anymore.
Don't apologize.
I-I wasn't thinking.
We're staying.
There are several things
I still need to ascertain
before moving on.
I intend to avenge
Izayoi's murder.
Will you help me?
[ASAHINA]
Cool. Are we good?
[USAMI] If I can hook up the
network cable, we're golden.
Now cross your fingers and
let's make some magic happen!
Come on, baby! Make momma proud!
Oh! Yeah!
We have connectivity!
Well that was easy.
[USAMI] Hailing frequencies
are open, Captain.
[NAEGI] Um, hello?
Can anyone hear me? This is--
[VOICE]
Read you loud and clear.
[NAEGI]
Byakuya?
Pleasure to hear from you.
Even if you do appear
a bit harried.
What's wrong?
Ah. Aren't you on trial
or some nonsense?
Things are complicated.
[TOGAMI]
Hm.
I'll need a bit more detail
than that, please.
So, a Mutual Killing game?
Wait, you-you didn't know?
But Monokuma told us
it was being televised,
just like last time.
I assure you, there has
been no such program.
It would be very intensive.
I don't believe the Remnants
have the wherewithal these days.
[gasps]
[TOGAMI]
No. Scratch that.
One of my little birds
reported back.
A Future Foundation
peacekeeping squad
is en route to a certain
island as we speak.
But, for some reason,
none of the other branches
have been informed.
Are they headed where
I think they are?
Indeed. Jabberwock Island.
[NAEGI] But... who would
possibly send them there?
The peacekeeping squad answers
directly to the Vice Chairman.
Ergo, we may reasonably deduce
whatever the meeting's outcome.
Kyosuke Munakata means to treat
the inhabitants of said island
as Remnants of Despair.
So everyone here's in danger!
[TOGAMI] I think we may further
postulate a connection
between this operation and
what's happening to you.
As you might imagine,
I don't like this one bit.
I thought it best to deploy
my own forces.
They shall reach
you momentarily.
[NAEGI]
Thank you. Just... be careful.
[TOGAMI]
I'll let Fuwaka into the loop.
Kirigiri is there
with you, correct?
Yep! It's time for the 78th
graduating class to reunite!
[NAEGI]
Well, mostly.
There's someone
we're forgetting.
[TOGAMI] I would not
call this a good time.
Honestly, we're just
glad you're coming.
We can hold out.
[TOGAMI] I meant for Monokuma
and "his excellency,"
Vice Chairman Munakata.
You're quick on your
feet, tenacious,
and singularly fortunate.
I'd sooner cavort with sharks
than risk making
an enemy of you.
Good luck.
[USAMI] Your party has
been disconnected.
[ASAHINA]
Hm.
He was so reassuring.
That was nice of him, huh?
Yeah, must be turning
over a new leaf.
The guy still has a way
with words, though!
[ASAHINA, NAEGI laugh]
You heard the man.
The Foundation is in danger.
Round up all present and
fully vetted members!
[AGENTS]
Sir!
[AGENT A] Excuse me,
but why didn't you tell him?
[TOGAMI] What?
About Miaya Gekkogahara?
Yes, sir. Naegi told
you she was with them.
That she in fact facilitated
the emergency call.
And yet, according to our intel,
Gekkogahara is dead.
[TOGAMI]
I am familiar with the report.
Clearly we're dealing
with an imposter.
Troubling, yes.
But we dare not expose her
while she's so close to them.
Who knows what she might do.
For now, the best course
of action is to let her be
and focus on the mastermind.
You don't think they're
one and the same, sir?
Given the Remnants' weakened
state, that may very well be.
Only one person has the
resources to orchestrate this.
Monaka Towa, who's
currently below the radar
somewhere in Towa City.
I'll wager she's our maestro.
Fortunately, we already
have people there.
No! Stop! Leave me alone!
Don't come any closer.
No! Please!
Now, now, Touko.
Everyone has to bathe.
You don't wanna stink!
[FUKAWA] Wh-What if I do?
Maybe I like how I smell.
[FUKAWA sniffing]
[KOMARU]
Gotcha!
--[KOMARU laughing]
--[FUKAWA squealing]
[KOMARU]
Hey! Quit squirming!
Oh! It's Master Byakuya!
Coming, sire!
Oh well. So much for
that idea, I guess.
[NAEGI]
We're all in this together.
And that's how we can survive.
With my friend by my side,
however bad things get,
we'll move forward
one step at a time.
[NAEGI] I may not know
what's waiting for us,
but...
[FUKAWA chuckling]
[NAEGI]
...we'll keep going.
Come what may.
[NAEGI]
That's what hope does.
It charges ahead.
[HINATA]
Boring.