[bang]
[yelps]
What the--?
What made that noise?
[KIRIGIRI]
Yeah, don't help me or anything.
How did you get here?
What're you even doing?
Call it a rescue mission.
One I thought would
be fairly obvious.
[chuckles]
[NAEGI]
Uh.
Sorry, but uh,
you have a little
something on your head.
You need to eat something.
We'll talk afterward.
You're a life saver!
There, see?
And just like that he's
back at full throttle.
Well, I don't know about
all that, but I guess,
bein' rescued does kinda put
a little spring in my step.
I have to say, optimism
definitely becomes you.
[ASAHINA crying]
[NAEGI]
Why?
You could have...
Why didn't you say something?!
[NAEGI]
Kirigiri...
Kyoko, no!
Not her.
[microphone hums]
[MUNAKATA]
Makoto Naegi.
If you're awake,
I assume you've discovered what
Kirigiri's Forbidden Action was.
Do you understand now?
Do you see the truth?
Your platitudes are useless.
[MUNAKATA]
It's time to cast them aside.
Time to settle once and
for all who's Hope is real.
Yours or mine.
Whatever happens next,
promise not to turn
your back on Hope.
I'm on your side.
Don't ever forget that.
[ASAHINA crying]
Wait, what're you--?
I'm going to confront Munakata.
Once and for all.
This bloodshed has to end.
The man's insane!
Do me a favor. I'd like
you to stay with Asahina.
So that's it?
You're walking away?
You're just gonna leave
Kirigiri's body here?
I thought the two of you were
supposed to be friends!
She's dead!
How can you brush something
like this off so easily?
I'm not just brushing it off.
I adored her.
She saved my life
more than once.
She kept her Forbidden
Action secret
so I wouldn't do...
something rash.
She died protecting
me from myself.
Kirigiri entrusted me
with her last hope.
So I'll fight. I'll push
forward to honor her.
Go for it.
I believe in you.
Give it all you've got.
Wait here.
Whatever happens next,
promise not to turn
your back on Hope.
Don't you worry. It's what I do.
Blind optimism.
[YUKIZOME crying]
[YUKIZOME]
I tried... I did.
By the time I got here,
they were...
Who...? Who would
do such a thing?
Why does this keep happening?
When is it going to stop?
Talk to me, Kyosuke.
What can we do to end all this?
How can we annihilate Despair?
[MUNAKATA]
You leave that to me.
[NAEGI]
Perk up. You're far from alone.
The Hope you carry was
given to you by everyone.
[MUNAKATA] If I must be the last
soul alive on earth, so be it.
Despair shall be vanquished.
[NAEGI] That's how it works,
how Hope gets passed on.
[MUNAKATA] Despair infects
and spreads like a virus.
Every potential host must die.
Makoto Naegi, this is
an act of compassion.
[NAEGI]
Munakata, one way or another....
[MUNAKATA]
I will save you.
[NAEGI]
...I will stop you.
[MUNAKATA]
So you've come.
[NAEGI]
That's right.
No second guessing. No stalling.
[MUNAKATA] I've never had
the luxury of uncertainty.
[NAEGI] There's no point
in us killing each other.
I've come to ask for your help.
We can end this game together.
[MUNAKATA]
Your words carry no weight.
I've told you this.
We're dancing in circles here.
You couldn't be more wrong.
What door could he
possibly want me to choose?
[MITARAI]
How can someone be so strong?
And why am I so weak?
I'm never gonna be worth a damn.
Oh, Kyoko...
[MUNAKATA] Is this where
you'd prefer to end it?
[NAEGI]
So close.
[MUNAKATA]
Hmph.
[MUNAKATA] If you intend to
take your quarry by surprise,
don't leave a trail of blood.
I'm not done.
What? Come on!
Doesn't seem to work.
I'd say your notorious lucky
streak has run its course.
[MUNAKATA coughing]
Damn! Where's he gone now?
[yells]
Damn you, Makoto Naegi.
Why'd you stop?
You can't kill me, can you?
I knew you would be
drawn to this place.
After all, we've
been here before.
The first time,
you let me get away.
And when you cornered me
in the Monitoring room,
you broke the glass to get in.
I found out your
Forbidden Action.
You can't open doors.
That's the reason you
can't kill me right now.
If you did, you'd be
trapped in here.
Now then, can we please talk?
[MUNAKATA]
There's no point.
Listen, I'll make
you a deal, all right?
Hear me out and I'll open
the door. I promise.
[MUNAKATA]
Enough! You're the enemy!
No, I'm not! Believe me!
[MUNAKATA] When did Despair
first get its hooks into you?
Was it the Mutual Killing
Game at Hope's Peak
that seduced you into darkness?
[NAEGI]
No.
Listen, I'm not on
the side of Despair!
Don't lie to me.
We shouldn't have been at odds.
We can beat this...
Together... As a team.
You keep saying that.
Need I remind you while
you paid lip service
to vacuous platitudes,
your friend Kirigiri died!
You still don't get it?
Someone you loved gave her life
upholding your naïve ideals!
Despair must die.
Doesn't matter who
the mastermind is.
I will do whatever must
be done to thwart them.
No sacrifice is too dear.
No cost too great.
That is true Hope!
That's not true.
That isn't Hope!
Listen to yourself!
All you're talking about is
ending Despair, that's it!
Even if that's possible,
it's not the same!
You've got tunnel vision.
Despair's all you can see.
Where's Hope? It's not even
part of the equation!
Don't turn this around.
Chairman Tengan
told me everything.
This is not the time or place
for a mental sparring
match, Chairman.
Which one of them is
the actual Attacker?
[TENGAN]
As I've said, if you're asking,
I have no choice but
to answer honestly.
There's more than one.
We're all of us responsible.
The entire Foundation.
In a manner of speaking, every
single member is the Attacker.
[gasps]
[TENGAN] Me, Naegi,
Sakakura, even Yukizome.
None of us are exempt.
How does it feel, friend?
Even the love of your
life was tainted.
Not one soul is left
uncorrupted by Despair.
Does that change your tactic?
Will you still do everything in
your power to annihilate it?
[MUNAKATA]
Is that...? Is that true?
I'm afraid so.
[MUNAKATA] In my heart, I know
what Tengan said was true.
All of us are tainted.
In the end, even
Yukizome gave in.
[MUNAKATA] When the
children died, she asked me,
"Who could do such a thing?"
And I was fool.
She answered her own
question in a photograph.
She was the one responsible.
When did it happen?
When did she first succumb?
I once believed her immune.
[MUNAKATA]
It doesn't matter.
Every trace of
Despair shall burn.
Even the memory of it
will turn to ash.
[NAEGI] Stop talking like that!
She was a person!
She meant something to you.
I don't care what she did!
She's worth more!
You know nothing! Nothing!
[MUNAKATA] Nothing!
Nothing! Nothing! Nothing!
Nothing! Nothing!
[NAEGI]
Yes I do!
I know...
If Kirigiri had
turned to Despair...
...betrayed every last
one of us...
...I know, even if I had
to resort to killing her,
I would always be grateful
for the person she was.
I'd always think
of her as someone
I couldn't possibly
have lived without!
[YUKIZOME]
Kyosuke.
Say what you will,
Hope's Peak High School is
what brought us together.
Think about it, I bet we'd never
even have met otherwise.
Chisa...
When? How did it happen?
[screaming]
[MUNAKATA crying]
I'm sorry, Kyosuke.
[MUNAKATA]
Where did we go wrong?
How could I have known it
would all end up like this?
[door opens]
[ASAHINA]
Naegi!
Oh my God, are you okay?
You're not really
that good at waiting.
[ASAHINA grunts]
The killing is over!
Do you hear me?
I know who the Attacker is.
It's all here.