[tires screech]
[gasps]
[SEIKO] Come on,
little guy. You'll be fine.
[RURUKA]
Wow!
Are you like a genius
or something?
That stuff you gave my dog,
it totally saved his life!
[giggles]
So, uh, hey.
You can call me Ruruka.
[SEIKO]
Huh?
And what should I call you?
[SEIKO]
Huh? Finally.
[RURUKA]
Oh.
Seiko!
[SEIKO]
Huh?
I got snacks with
your name on 'em!
Seriously? You can't
eat sweets at all?
[SEIKO]
Mh-hm.
Sorry. Sugar's bad for me.
It causes the medicine I'm on
to have real awful side effects.
You can't even have a teeny
li'l bite every now and then?
I couldn't live like that.
That sucks. I love sweets.
Only thing better is getting
to share them with friends.
[SEIKO]
Wait. Am I your...?
Um, duh!
If you're askin' if you're
my friend, the answer is yes!
[SEIKO]
That's really...
[RURUKA]
Huh?
[SEIKO] Um, is there anything
I can help you out with?
I might not be able
to eat sweets,
but there's plenty of
stuff I can do!
Oh, wow! You mean that?
For realsies?
[SEIKO]
Back in the old days,
I think we sincerely
were friends.
But then, before long, I got
less out of it than I put in.
Ruruka started taking
advantage of me.
And now, here we are.
[SEIKO roaring]
[SEIKO growls]
[SEIKO]
Gotcha!
[SEIKO screams]
[SEIKO]
You laid a trap?
[SOHNOSUKE]
More of an art project.
I forged it from
a special alloy.
Hurts like a bitch, huh?
This is the part
where you die, Seiko.
I will kill you in the
name of deliciousness!
[coughs]
You wanna know what's
going on in my head?
You were a force
to reckon with.
Before you turned into a coward.
[TENGAN groans]
Your resolve was terrifying.
Then you tucked your tail
between your legs.
What happened?
Is that an actual question or
are you simply being rhetorical?
I took a good, hard
look at the impasse
our methods have brought us to.
We couldn't beat Despair.
[MUNAKATA]
Wrong. That's where I come in.
Is this what you
sacrificed Yukizome for?
[gasps]
[TENGAN]
Listen to me.
You've somehow got
it into your head
that annihilating the
Remnants is the same
as annihilating Despair.
Kill 'em all and that's
the end of it, yes?
Trust me, old friend.
Victory is not the
prerogative of war alone.
[NAEGI] Miss Gekkogahara.
I hope she'll be okay.
Hey, she's in better shape than
you or me, that's for sure.
[JUZO]
Yo.
'Parently we're doin'
this the hard way.
Make a break for it, Asahina.
You should know what
kinda girl I am by now.
Hey. Hold on. What're you doing?
[ASAHINA]
So, Mr. Man,
you used to be a Super High
School-Level Boxer, yeah?
What's a brick house like you
need with weapons? Lame.
I save my fists for opponents
who're worth a damn.
For you though? Nah.
Why are you even doing all this?
Dumb enough to stand
in the boss' way,
ya get taken off the board.
Munakata's the future!
[yells]
[What's the matter?
Just gonna run?
[sniffing]
What?
I'd know that sickeningly
sweet smell anywhere.
Someone didn't listen to me.
[RURUKA squeals]
Ah! Lookie what we have here!
Hey, hon! I could use
some lip balm.
Think you can whip that up?
[SEIKO] No problem.
I'll bring it tomorrow.
[RURUKA]
Thanks! You're a genius!
Ugh, bleh.
Pretty sure I'm coming down
with a case of the plague.
Got anything in there
I could take?
[SEIKO] Are you running a fever?
Coughing? Headache?
I can make you a
fast-acting remedy.
Well, that does it.
This exam will be the end of me.
It's been a crazy ride.
Don't s'pose there's
something you could do?
[SEIKO] Uh, sure.
What are best friends for?
Hang on. Umm.
Here! This is great for
memory and comprehension.
Um, hey, Ruruka?
So about this stuff.
It does perk you up, but you've
gotta use it in moderation.
[RURUKA]
Eh.
[RURUKA] Sure, I used to ask
her for help at first.
She offered, didn't she?
But things started to
change between us.
I was super good
at making sweets
and not once did she seem
the least bit interested.
They're practically the
only thing I do well.
She knew that and still refused
to acknowledge my talent.
Told you you couldn't hide!
[RURUKA]
No! Please! Leave me alone!
[SOHNOSUKE]
Ruruka!
Isn't that interesting.
[RURUKA whispers]
No problem.
If that's what you want.
Where is he going?
Oh, he just ran to
grab us a weapon
so we can finish
you off, no bigs.
Have'ta be careful not
to get too close to you,
even if we do suddenly have
the home field advantage,
so to speak.
Wh-What do you mean?
[giggles]
I think I've figured out
what your Forbidden
Action is, sugarplum.
Hey, right on the money!
Poor thing. Must've
been a real pain.
Not letting your shadow
get stepped on.
[growls]
[MUNAKATA]
Solely the prerogative of war?
[TENGAN]
You're young.
You think killing the
Remnants is the only option,
that wholesale slaughter
will give rise to Hope,
but your reasoning
is deeply flawed.
It's precisely that
line of thinking
that led to the
Kamukura Project.
Of course. I suspected as much.
[sighs]
And as long as
we're being candid,
only a fool would think of
it as the end all, be all.
I see it now.
In fact, I couldn't
be more certain.
It's you. You're the Attacker.
Obviously.
For what it's worth,
I had my doubts.
[HAGAKURE]
Naegi!
Please let me in!
They're-- They're tryin'
to kill me, man!
You don't want your ol' pal
to be Swiss cheese-- Ah!
See?
[SOHNOSUKE] Should I swallow
my pride as a blacksmith?
Uh! Damn it!
Bet they have no idea
I'm runnin' around out here
like a chicken with
its head cut off!
What is goin' on in there?
Wh--? What the hell?
[RURUKA] How did I
figure it out, you ask?
Elementary, my dear Watson!
I simply observed your
reaction to the lights.
When you saw them switch on,
your panic was unmistakable.
Oh, and I couldn't
help but notice
you kept avoiding
Yoi like poison.
Plus, why else would you
still be here listening to me?
It all fits. Sorry.
[RURUKA]
You know, I could let you go.
In fact, if you do
exactly as I say,
I might be willing
to bury the hatchet.
Just a nibble.
Yeah, no more polite refusals.
No more "Oh, but I can't."
Eat and you get to live.
[growls]
[SEIKO]
If I eat it, I'll die.
I've told you before.
Countless times.
[RURUKA]
Ugh. I swear.
Fine, whatever.
I'll just have to come up
with something else.
Hmm...
Got it!
Let's talk about Vice
Chairman Munakata.
[gasps]
Swear on your life
you'll kill him
and you're off the hook
with me and Sohnosuke.
Deal?
But... I-- You can't.
[RURUKA]
Look, we have nothing to do
with the Remnants
of Despair, okay?
I promise.
We're just of the opinion that
removing him from the equation
is the best way to
resolve this mess.
Self righteous bastard's
running the Foundation
into the ground.
He's gotta be dealt with.
I can't do it. I refuse! He--
[SEIKO]
He took me in.
Hope's Peak had thrown me out.
I was as good as dead.
And there he was, like a
guardian angel,
offering me a future just when
I thought my story was over.
[screaming]
No! Stay back!
[RURUKA]
Seiko. You used to be my hero.
It seemed like there was
nothing you couldn't do.
Whenever I needed something...
...all I had to do was ask.
I trusted you.
[SEIKO] I wanted--
I needed a friend. That's it.
Be my friend and I'd follow
you to Hell and back.
I gave you everything,
without question.
[RURUKA] I hate that it's
come to this. I really do.
[SEIKO]
Why did this have to happen?
Where did I go wrong?
[RURUKA] I asked for your help
because I believed in you.
[SEIKO]
I gave you whatever you wanted
because I wanted you to like me.
[RURUKA] I relied on you so much
because I looked up to you.
I wanted to be you.
[SEIKO]
You looked down your nose at me.
You always did.
I was a tool to you.
[SEIKO yells]
[SEIKO, RURUKA]
What happened?
Why did things
turn out this way?
[gasps]
[SEIKO chuckles]
[SEIKO yells]
[tires screching]
[USAMI]
We're back, ladies and germs!
Eh, maybe I should.
Just a little.
Okie dokie! Let's go! Round Two!
[USAMI] Fair warning, folks,
this is gonna be big!
You probably oughta duck!
What?
We gotta get down!
[USAMI]
Fire in the hole!
[USAMI] Boom! Now you
probably oughta run!
I mean, a girl's gotta
keep herself entertained
somehow, right?
Naegi, hop on!
Uh, yeah. Good call.
Wait! Son of a--!
You gotta be
kiddin' me with this.
I'm startin' to severely hate
this guy's lucky streak.
Can't last forever.
Have you learned
anything useful?
Yes. Quite a bit.
Ahh. Well, good for you.
So do we have a plan yet?
I need to locate and
examine Gozu's body.
It'll tell me what I need to
know about the Attacker's MO.
Okay.
They said you were cold,
but holy crap.
[MUNAKATA]
Point one:
This base's existence
is virtually unknown.
And point two:
Among those in the loop,
very few possess the means of
cutting us off from the outside.
It makes sense if you
look past the why.
How is it a man of your
stature comes to align himself
to the Remnants
in the first place?
If that's a question,
guess I have to answer.
I'm not on their side.
Though of course, I realize
what it must look like.
A logical conclusion
on your part,
albeit rather simplistic
for a mind so sharp.
This is not the time or place
for a mental sparring
match, Chairman.
Which of them is
the actual Attacker?
[TENGAN]
As I've said, if you're asking,
I have no choice but
to answer honestly.
[inaudible]
[MUNAKATA]
Is that--? Is that true?
I'm afraid so.
[MUNAKATA]
Hmph.
[MUNAKATA chuckles]
[MUNAKATA]
So be it then.
Hardly matters now.
I am beyond second
guessing myself.
Munakata, wait!
[MUNAKATA screaming]
You know absolutely
nothing, old man.
You don't know me, and you don't
know what I have in store.
Perhaps not.
But you, my friend, know nothing
about the nature of Hope.
[SEIKO]
Look at me.
What did I do?
How did I screw this up?
I'm useless... Useless.
Why the hell couldn't
I do something?
Why couldn't I save them?
I wanted to help.
That's the reason
behind everything I do.
[SEIKO] I just tried to be
a friend. Was that so bad?
[music plays]
[SEIKO]
Seiko. Seiko Kimura.
Cool! Then that's what
I'm gonna call you!
Here! I actually made it myself!
See ya. Seiko!
[RURUKA giggles]
[MUNAKATA grunting]
[MUNAKATA]
Very well. Time to end this.