[laughing]
[MONOKUMA] Hey there,
kids, it's Monokuma!
Since your brains
have probably got
the storage capacity of a gnat,
I'm here to help make sure
everybody's up to speed!
That's right! It's time for
a filler-recap episode!
Kidding! We wouldn't
do that to ya!
This'll just be a quick
summary. Promise.
So basically, Naegi
pulled some strings
for the Remnants of Despair and
was brought before the leaders
of the Future Foundation
to answer for it.
No sooner had they all
gathered to discuss
their questionable
comrade's fate...
And wham-o!
A brand new Mutual
Killing Game began!
Board members started
droppin' like flies!
Some lucky mortician's gonna
make enough mulah to retire on!
In the midst of all this,
Munakata killed Chairman Tengan
and underwent a
startling transformation.
To make matters worse,
Naegi caught wind of
an ominous prophecy.
Before long, Glasses McDorkface,
excuse me, Togami,
showed up with reinforcements,
hoping to join in on the fun!
What now, you ask?
Anyone's guess, really!
So kick back, relax,
and enjoy the carnage!
Whoa! What the hell's goin' on?
Ah!
[HAGAKURE]
HQ!
They... They could
survive that, right?
Great, yeah. Earthquake. Sure.
[RURUKA groans]
Whatever.
The sooner I get outta here,
the sooner it won't matter.
[gasps]
What the shit?
I think we're far enough
from the danger now.
So remind me again why we
didn't go through the exit?
I mean it had to have
been a trap, right?
It certainly wasn't a way out.
[MITARAI] I had a feeling.
But how can you be so sure?
Well, to be fair, that
passage would've led us
to the building's exterior.
Technically. But we
couldn't have escaped.
Not with our lives.
We're under the ocean.
[MITARAI]
W-We're what?!
[KIRIGIRI] Trust me. This is not
the building we started in.
It's a carbon copy.
Identical in every way.
But directly beneath
the original.
[KIRIGIRI]
If you recall,
we were gassed in the conference
room when this began.
In all likelihood we were
moved while unconscious,
and deposited in the
room's underwater duplicate
so no one would suspect a thing.
But that's a ridiculous amount
of effort, and for what?
It becomes worthwhile
if the aim is to confuse.
Your disbelief is proof
the tactic works.
[KIRIGIRI] At first, I had my
doubts it was even possible.
But once we got our
bearings after waking up,
I noticed the mark on the door
from earlier had vanished.
Okay, but then why
put us in the ocean?
To keep outsiders from
intervening, I should think.
Yes, of course.
This all points to
the Vice Chairman.
He's been closely involved with
the building's construction
from the ground up.
He couldn't have
failed to notice.
It's only logical. Everything
about this situation favors him.
[USAMI] Switching to...
Elimination Mode!
[MUNAKATA] Despair has
taken everything from me.
No one else will suffer.
No one else will endure
what I've gone through.
Despair... will be eradicated.
[MUNAKATA]
This would appear to be its CPU.
The actions I've
taken are not wrong.
In the end, I shall become Hope.
Hey, hey. Looks like you got one
of the skeevy little bastards.
[JUZO]
What's the matter? Let's go.
[MUNAKATA] To that purpose,
no sacrifice is too dear.
[MITARAI]
I don't know what to say.
Can he really be the mastermind?
[KIRIGIRI] For now, let's just
find Naegi and the others.
Uh. Seriously? I, uh, can't
see how he'd help much.
I can understand why
you might think that.
Granted, Naegi might not seem
like much a first glance,
but when push comes to shove,
he's the strongest human
being I've ever known.
Bar none.
He's optimistic. He always
puts his friends first.
And he couldn't give up
if his life depended on it.
I believe in the man
with all my heart.
See, there was a time when...
...when if he hadn't
been around, I--
Hm?
[ASAHINA chuckles]
[KIRIGIRI clears throat]
[NAEGI]
Wow. Under the sea, huh?
Somebody went to
a lotta trouble.
[KIRIGIRI]
Evidently.
You said Togami was en
route with reinforcements?
[NAEGI]
Mhm.
It's been long enough now
that he should be at
the real HQ as we speak.
What if there's traps?
What if Togami's hurt?
Oh, God. It'd be all my fault.
What do you mean?
I was told...
...someone would die,
all because of me.
Don't start down that path.
Why would you think that?
Did Munakata say something?
You know, up until now,
I was confident I could be
useful in any situation.
Here though, I'm sunk.
There's nothing I can do.
Munakata was right.
My words don't carry any
real weight. I'm just--
[KIRIGIRI]
Letting him get to you.
Your words lift people up.
Give them something
to pin their hopes on.
That's certainly what
they've done for me.
Have faith in yourself, Naegi.
We need your words.
We need your optimism.
Your hope is infectious.
If ever you lose sight of
yourself, just look to us.
We'll remind you who you are.
It's the least we can do.
[ASAHINA chuckles]
Those wounds don't look so hot.
We should find you
a first aid kit.
[JUZO]
Hey, so...
What's on your mind?
Well, uh. Kimura's been killed.
Izayoi got poisoned, too.
Oh, along with Kizakura.
I-- I just thought
you ought to know.
[MUNAKATA]
Tengan as well.
Uh?
No joke?
I killed him myself.
Right. Sure.
Hey, that's good! This is
what we wanted, isn't it?
Purify the Foundation.
Heh. About damn time.
This baby's in your
hands now, chief.
You've been promoted.
No one in their right
mind's gonna contest it.
The revolution's over! And
the spoils of war are all yours!
I'll help, of course.
We're gonna fix the
Future Foundation.
After that, the world!
[MUNAKATA]
The world, you say?
Hey, Sakakura. We go back.
You've been at my side
for years, in fact;
since we were students.
Uh, yeah.
We had our share of good times.
The two of us, and
Yukizome, of course.
Eyes always on the future.
Three friends intimately bound
together by the same ideals.
Our mentors were supportive.
Tengan always found the
time to give me advice.
I held firm that the
world could change.
That I could be the
one to change it.
That conviction hasn't left me.
It's as strong as ever.
Yeah, sure.
Hey, it's strong in me too,
you know, always has been.
Backin' you up's been the
whole point of my life.
I take a lotta pride in
throwin' down for your ideals.
I know you do. And you're
right, my friend.
Without your unwavering support,
I would never have
made it this far.
Look, I...
There's somethin' I gotta
get off my chest, okay?
To be totally honest with you--
Enough.
--[thud]
--[gasps]
Kyosuke...
What the hell, man?
Why would you do this?
You know why.
You know exactly why.
Despair will pay for
making me kill you.
That I can promise.
Even the poor Chairman.
[NAEGI] Yeah, I know.
I saw him on the monitor.
Before he died, he left
a kind of message.
"I entrust the Hope
of the world to you."
[MITARAI]
The Hope of the world...
What do you think he meant?
[RURUKA] Good riddance.
The ape had it coming.
[JUZO]
What the hell, man?
Why would you do this?
[MUNAKATA] You know why.
You know exactly why.
[RURUKA] Everyone gets
betrayed in the end.
It was just Sakakura's turn.
The man was a fool.
Just as well, really.
I wasn't wrong to do what I did.
You're sure no one's
gonna stumble across it?
[SOHNOSUKE]
Absolutely.
They'll never even
know that door exists.
Yeah, but still, they
might find it on accident.
There's no reason to be afraid.
If they start pokin' around, all
they're gonna find are my traps.
Yoi, please. Never betray me.
Hey, quit with that stuff.
You know I'd never do
anything to break your heart.
You're my first priority.
I care more about you
than I do myself.
I know you do.
You don't have it in you
to throw me to the wolves.
But I'm scared.
You're the one person I--
If you ever lied to me...
[SOHNOSUKE grunts]
[music plays]
...I don't think
I could go on living.
I-I'm sorry.
There's no other way.
I can't take that
chance with you.
I-- I know it's not fair, but...
...I love y--
No worries. Life isn't fair.
I understand. I love you.
It's okay.
[RURUKA]
Oh, God.
What now? The time
limit is almost up.
[RURUKA]
I'll survive this.
You may be gone, Yoi,
but I'm not alone.
When I get out of here,
I can make other
friends, tons of them!
It'll be easy. All I
have to do is stay alive.
Forever. And ever
and ever. On my own.
Never let anyone betray me.
[MITARAI, NAEGI yelp]
[ASAHINA] Okay.
That oughta do it, I think.
[MITARAI]
Wow.
[NAEGI]
Sorry.
It's mostly my fault she has
so much upper body strength.
[ASAHINA, NAEGI,
MITARAI laughing]
We're almost at
the time limit.
Let's see the Attacker try 'n
bust their way in here now.
[KIRIGIRI] Nice work, but we may
not be as safe as you think.
Uh?
I see what you mean.
Whoever it is has complete
control over this whole place.
What's a simple
barricade gonna do?
I suppose there's no real
way to be absolutely sure.
Naegi. Listen.
Whatever happens next,
promise not to turn
your back on Hope.
I'm on your side.
Don't ever forget that.
Yeah, I know you're
always with me.
I believe with all my heart
we're gonna win this thing.
Look at us! How can we lose?
[ASAHINA]
Mh-hm.
[music plays]
[gasps]
We're still alive.
I think we did it!
No one's been killed!
[ASAHINA] Looks like we
made it through, huh?
Yeah. Your barricade
worked like a charm.
[NAEGI gasps]
God, please no.
Her Forbidden Action.
Kirigiri! Kirigiri!
[NAEGI]
This-- This isn't happening.
But she knew it was
the fourth time limit!
[NAEGI]
Why?
You could have--
Why didn't you say something?!
[NAEGI]
Kirigiri...
Kyoko, no!
Not her.
[microphone hums]
[MUNAKATA]
Makoto Naegi.
If you're awake,
I assume you've discovered what
Kirigiri's Forbidden Action was.
Do you understand now?
Do you see the truth?
Your platitudes are useless.
[MUNAKATA]
It's time to cast them aside.
Time to settle once and
for all whose Hope is real.
Yours or mine.
Whatever happens next,
promise not to turn
your back on Hope.
I'm on your side.
Don't ever forget that.