[TOHKA]
Shido! What's in here?
Is it a date?
Tell me!
[NARRATOR]
Upon Tohka's arrival
in this strange new world,
she was immediately
faced with a challenge.
She could choose
to fight against
the appetite of her
growing curiosity,
or feed it generously with love.
And today, Shido's wallet is
also feeling conflicted.
[FEMALE CLERK]
Thank you! Please come again!
[SHIDO]
Here you go.
Ooohhh...
Is this a test?
Am I about to fail?
Uh, no. It's for you.
Stop drooling.
Wow!
[TOHKA chewing]
Is this one of
those date things?
[SHIDO]
No, it's bread.
Okay.
Is that another name for "date"?
I don't understand how
something so delicious
can't be called a date.
You can call it
one if you want to.
Fascinating. Even though
this was delicious,
it's still not good enough
to be called a date.
And so the mystery continues.
There's one!
[SHIDO] Not quite!
All these persons.
Where'd they come from?
Is this war?
If that's the case,
I better attack before the
Mecha-Mecha Squad gets here.
No, wait! You don't
want to do that!
[TOHKA] Why are you stopping
me from saving us?
[SHIDO] I'm not!
There's nothing to save us from.
No one is trying to hurt us!
[BOY]
Look, Mama.
See? I threw it in
the trash all by myself!
[MOTHER] Wow!
What a good boy you are!
[TOHKA giggles]
[TOHKA] What about right now?
This moment? Is this a date?
[SHIDO] Not really.
But you're getting closer.
[TOHKA] Dates are
complicated matters.
Ah! Look! That thing
over there looks yummy!
How in the world are
you still hungry?
Am I cray or is that
Shido with a new girl?
Omigosh does that mean
he's cheating on Tonomachi?
That's so lame.
[ORIGAMI] That woman.
I know she's a Spirit.
But there's no spatial quake.
Sergeant Origami reporting.
A-0613. Need an observation
device immediately.
Outrageous!
I can't believe humans each
such amazingly delicious things!
Heh, heh. Oh hey, Tohka.
What happened after
you left yesterday?
Same thing as usual.
I swing my sword around some.
I blast the artillery.
In the end, my body disappeared
naturally like it always does.
[SHIDO]
Disappeared?
[TOHKA] Yes, I go to a world
different from this one.
It's a dark space.
Once I get there,
I just fall asleep.
So you mean, when you
wake up, you come here?
[TOHKA] Well, I don't
wake up on my own.
It's more like by force.
And it has nothing to
do with what I want.
I'm just pulled here.
Usually, anyway.
[SHIDO] By force?
Then Spirits don't cause
spatial quakes on purpose.
They must just be accidents.
By "usually" you mean
today was different?
How would I know?
Please tell me.
Look, that might
actually be the reason
there wasn't a
spatial quake today.
You're too persistent.
Besides, I have important things
to do, like find more food!
Tohka, come on. Wait!
I should've brought more money.
[RYOKO] It looks like
she's a 98.5 percent match.
That's way too high to be
a coincidence, of course.
But why is she here?
She isn't wearing her
Spirit armor right now.
If we want to attack,
this is it.
[RYOKO]
Think about where you are.
You know we can't
afford to be reckless.
[TOHKA] What kind
of place is this?
[SHIDO]
Uh, an expensive one.
I don't know what that means.
I'm going in.
No! Wait, hold on!
[TONOMACHI]
Well, if it isn't Shido!
[SHIDO]
Tonomachi?
[TONOMACHI]
Hmm...
What do we have here?
That's some hot action.
How did you manage to
pull that kind of tail
without me knowing
about it, huh?
I'm a little jealous.
Yeah, a lot has happened
lately, I guess.
[TONOMACHI] Whoa! And straight
off the top of the shelf!
It's cool, man.
My lady's got some pretty
expensive taste, too.
Check it out!
[SHIDO] Right.
His virtual girlfriend.
[TONOMACHI]
Listen, I want to help you.
Someone gave me these
tickets but I think they'll
impress your fancy new girlie
and help you score later.
You're welcome in advance!
Let me know how it goes.
See you later, bud!
[GIRL]
How are you today?
[SHIDO] Reine?
What? Wha--? How--?
What are you doing here?
Checking on Princess.
We have to make sure we're not
at risk of another
spatial quake.
She's been waiting for
you right over there.
Over here, Shido!
Why are you so late?
Sorry.
[GIRL] What's up, Kittens?
You ready to order?
Kotori?! What? Wh--
[clang]
Hmm... This looks so good;
but so does that one.
I wonder which of
these two is the date.
Hey, if you guys can't decide,
I have a suggestion for you.
The "How 'Bout This?"
[BOTH]
What does that one come with?
Whoa. Should be called
'What's With All This?'
Yum! Thank you!
It tastes so outrageous!
It must be a date!
What are you trying
to pull here, Kotori?
"Thank you,"
works, too.
We're pulling out all the
stops to help you score,
'cause I'm awesome.
But we also have some
business to discuss.
As soon as you guys leave,
I need you to head
south of the station.
But what for? That's
just a residential area.
Okay then!
I trust you've got this!
Now. Let's get
this date started.
[KANNAZUKI]
Checking AI analysis.
Use shop-type E-5963.
[MALE CREW MEMBER]
E-5963. Roger.
Open the main gate!
[TOHKA]
What's that?
Let's eat it!
It looks so yummy!
[SHIDO]
No, you can't eat them!
Well, you can; but not those.
[TOHKA] Wow!
They even have red ones!
They're so fast!
[SHIDO] Yeah, the red ones
are three times as fast
as the others.
Don't know why they'd
be here, though.
Uh--
What the heck is all that?
[KAWAGOE]
Congratulations!
What is going on here?
You two are this
shopping arcade's
one hundred thousandth visitors!
So we have a special
gift for both of you.
Everything you eat here
today will be free!
[GROUP]
Congratulations!
Thanks, but I don't get it.
I've never seen
one of those before!
Hey, wait, Tohka!
Come back here!
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Nice work, Kawagoe.
[KANNAZUKI] All right.
Fried food team,
get ready for service.
Fish cake and shaved ice team,
approach customers.
Noodle team, why was
the delivery late?
Do you think we're
going to be okay?
Shin and Tohka are moving in.
Glad to see we're all ready
and prepared for action.
[REINE]
Speak for yourself.
[ORIGAMI]
The signal's jammed.
[RYOKO]
Origami, can you hear me?
I've managed to squeeze
mobilization orders
from the higher ups.
Meet us at point
one hundred and one.
[ORIGAMI]
Roger that.
[TOHKA] Yummy! I can't
get over this food!
What's that? It looks amazing!
Oh, so does this!
Gimmie!
[SHIDO]
Slow down! Don't rush.
Eat as much as you
want. It's free.
How the hell did this happen?
[TOHKA] Shido?
I'm having fun. Are you?
Huh?
This has been such a great day
and I'm having a
wonderful time here.
But I'm worried
I'm the only one.
You seem upset.
Are you mad at me?
No way! Of course
I'm not mad at you!
[TOHKA]
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
In fact I'm in a great mood!
I've just had a lot
on my mind is all.
Promise you're
having a good time?
Best time ever!
I really hope you're
telling the truth.
I am. I swear.
I'm glad we came here today.
[gasps]
There's so much food
we have to try!
Let's get the most we
can out of this date!
Yeah. Let's.
--Great, come on!
--'Kay!
[SHIDO] Wherever you need
me to go, I'll follow!
Congratulations, you two!
You won the grand prize!
Two tickets to Dream Park,
redeemable any time! Woo!
I don't know what that means!
But it sounds like fun!
[SHIIZAKI] It's the most
fun you'll ever have!
What's this?
You've never been?
That's unheard of, you've
got to take her right now!
[SHIDO]
Dream Park?
[CROWD] Hey! Wow!
[SHIDO] Whoa!
[TOHKA] Look how
beautiful this place is!
What an adventure!
What kind of things
can we do in here?
[SHIDO]
Well, I don't know.
Do it! Do it! Do it!
Hey, I have an idea!
Let's not go in there! 'Kay?
I don't agree.
You told me that we could
go wherever I wanted today.
Shido.
Do you think I'll learn what
a date is behind those doors?
Something tells me
that's very possible.
But I don't think it's
a good idea today.
--Besides, we're not legal.
--I'm not ready to go yet.
How am I supposed to learn
if you won't let me
experience these things?
[RYOKO]
Origami, where are you?
What's happening?
The time to meet has passed.
[ORIGAMI] Currently surveying
the movements of the target.
Send an emergency arming device
to point zero eighty-eight,
one hundred seven.
[KAWAGOE] I can't
believe I'm seeing this.
Why didn't he bring
her in to do the deed?
[KOTORI] This isn't the
first time you've failed
with that tactic, is it Kawagoe?
[SHIIZAKI] Fact established,
and acknowledged.
Classic Shido.
He always insists on doing
everything in a proper order.
What's that? Rain?
[REINE] Strange.
There weren't any rain
clouds in the vicinity.
[KOTORI] Oh, well.
Maybe it's for the best.
[gasps]
Where did you bring me?
Is this the secret base
of the Mecha-Mecha Squad?
[SHIDO]
Of course not. Don't worry.
[TOHKA] Why can't I get you,
you unruly chicken!
Shido! Tell this
thing to cooperate!
I told you. This
is a really tough one.
You have to
have a strategy,
and yelling through
the glass doesn't work.
Fine! Then how?
[SHIDO]
This one should be easy.
It's sticking up.
That's not the one I want.
I want the chicken.
Okay. Well, maybe there's
another one like it somewhere.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
I can get you whichever
prize you want!
Come on! Pick one!
[SHIDO]
Maybe that one.
I've got it!
Listen closely. I'll
use this button over here.
You use the one on
your side there.
Let go when I give the signal.
It's worth a shot.
[SHIDO]
Wait for it. Wait for it.
Wait for it.
Now!
Let it go, Tohka!
Chicken!
Hold on! It still
hasn't dropped yet!
[SHIDO] I'm so sorry;
that was totally my fault.
I didn't give good instructions.
Drop the chicken!
Please drop it! Why
won't you listen to me?
Shido and I worked
so hard on this.
Drop it! Please!
It's okay.
I'm begging you!
Drop it, you have to!
Please!
[chuckles]
[BOTH]
We did it!
[TOHKA] Question. What method
do those use to transform?
[SHIDO] Actually,
trains don't transform.
[TOHKA] What?
So they use fusion?
[SHIDO] Well, they do
connect to each other.
[TOHKA]
Oh, wow!
Thank you. I had
so much fun today.
[SHIDO] Good. Me too.
Thanks for coming.
[TOHKA] I am a
little disappointed
that we didn't get to
explore Dream Park.
[SHIDO] Oh, it's
totally overrated!
[TOHKA]
If you say so. But Shido?
The day is almost over and
I still didn't see a date.
Can you tell me
what one is like?
[SHIDO] A date is just
when a girl and a boy
go out and have a
good time together.
You can't actually see one.
[TOHKA]
Oh, that makes sense!
Well in that case, I would say
we had a wonderful date today!
[SHIDO]
Uh, sure.
[TOHKA]
I like dates. They're nice.
Not good. I can't
believe I'm seeing this.
A Spirit shows up
without a spatial quake
and then connects
with a human boy.
Permission to shoot, Miss?
[RYOKO] Not yet. Still
waiting to hear from the top.
This is a very
unusual situation.
No one's been evacuated.
We'll just have to wait and see.
Point Alpha here.
What happened?
What?
We've got permission to shoot?
[TOHKA] All the humans
were very kind today.
[SHIDO] No one tried
to kill you, did they?
I knew you'd be okay.
[TOHKA]
Yeah. You're right.
I never knew the
world was so kind,
so much fun, and so beautiful.
I love it here.
And now, I understand why the
Mecha-Mecha Squad is after me.
Because whenever I
appear in this world,
something bad happens.
I ruin something beautiful.
I ruin your world.
[SHIDO]
That's not true.
So listen, I've been thinking
and it's better if I
don't exist anymore.
[SHIDO]
Don't say that!
We're fine!
There was no spatial
quake today, was there?
You didn't ruin anything!
[TOHKA]
Yes, but that doesn't mean
there won't be one
the next time I appear.
Once I go back and fall asleep,
I won't be able
to control myself.
[SHIDO] Fine! Then I guess
you just can't go back!
--Huh?
--Have you ever even tried?
Just once. Just
try staying here!
[TOHKA] Even if I did,
there are so many things
I don't know about this world.
[SHIDO] I'll teach you
whatever you don't know!
[TOHKA] Then I'd need food
and a place to sleep.
What if something happens
we're not prepared for?
[SHIDO] I'm going
to take care of you!
If something comes up
that we need to deal with,
we'll deal with it.
[TOHKA]
Are you sure?
Am I even allowed to be here?
Is it okay for me to be
alive in this world?
[SHIDO]
Yes! It is!
[TOHKA] You're the only one
who would say that to me.
Humans like the
Mecha-Mecha Squad,
they don't want to risk it.
They don't want something
as dangerous as me nearby.
[SHIDO]
I don't care about them!
Even if everyone
else rejects you,
it doesn't change the
fact that I accept you
and I don't want you to leave!
Take my hand.
That's the only job
you have right now.
[RYOKO] Distance:
Five hundred twelve, fifteen.
Wind direction:
Forty-point-eight.
Wind speed: zero-point-four.
Temperature:
twenty-four degrees,
RH: fifty-two point eight.
We're all clear.
[gunshot]
[SHIDO] Tohka!
[TOHKA yells]
What are you doing?
[thud]
[RYOKO]
Origami? Origami, come in!
Origami?
Shido.
I thought maybe if you were
here for me it would be okay.
Might be hard, but I'd be able
to do it with you by my side.
I can get through anything
when I'm with you.
But it doesn't matter.
It's no use!
You're gone now!
I'm on my own.
This world has rejected me!
Adonai Merek!
Sandalphon!
Halvanhelv!
How dare you!
How dare you reject me!
[RYOKO] No way.
Origami, retreat immediately!
Support troops, where are you?
Origami? Do you read me?
So it was you.
You're the one who did it.
You killed my only friend.
And with him, my soul.
Just admit it.
[ORIGAMI] Yes.
I killed Shido Itsuka.
[TOHKA] Kill her.
She must pay for
what she's done.
She must die.
[SHIIZAKI] It doesn't look
like a pulse or heart rate
is registering for Shido.
[NAKATSUGAWA] The spatial
quake alarm is going off.
This can't be good.
[MIKIMOTO] Resident evacuation
is still at seven percent.
[KOTORI] We're lucky there
aren't many houses nearby,
but at this rate, the whole town
will be decimated
within minutes.
If she were a knight, she would
have earned a passing grade,
but if she gets herself
killed as a princess,
then she's obviously not
worth our concern. Hm?
[KAWAGOE] Excuse me, Commander.
What have we heard about Shido?
[KOTORI] Oh, I wouldn't
worry too much about him.
My brother won't be finished
off by something like that.
[GROUP] Huh?
There it is.
[SHIDO] Hot! Hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Huh?
Where am I?
[MINOWA] Commander,
what-- What do we do now?
[KOTORI]
I already told you.
Even if Shido dies, he'll be
able to start a new game.
So what the heck are
you dragging ass for?
Get down there and
recover him immediately.
No one else is able to stop her.
It has to be him.
That's right. With the method
we decided to save for last.
[ORIGAMI] I did it.
I killed someone.
[TOHKA screams]
[ORIGAMI]
I'm like them. The Spirits.
We're the same.
[TOHKA screams]
[ORIGAMI yells]
We must end this.
[ORIGAMI]
Dad? Mom?
I'm sorry.
Shido. I promise to avenge you.
[SHIDO screams]
What? He's alive!
Shido? Is it really you?
Yeah. Yeah, I think it is!
Thank you!
Thank you for coming back!
Don't cry.
Everything's okay now.
Tohka! What the heck is that?
[TOHKA] I accidentally
unsheathed Halvanhelv.
I have to find
somewhere to release it!
[SHIDO] No! Hold on!
You definitely can't do that!
[TOHKA]
Then what should I do?
It's already reached
its critical state!
[KOTORI]
Shido, can you hear me?
Now is the time to use that
method I taught you earlier.
It's the only way you'll
be able to save her.
All right, Tohka, listen to me.
--We have to kiss now, okay?
--We what?
Uh, never mind.
Forget it, I'm sorry.
There has to be another way.
No, I just don't
know what a kiss is.
--Huh?
--Teach me and I'll do it!
Um, 'kay. It's where we put
our lips together and then we--
I'm so sorry!
They told me this was the
only way I could reverse it!
Just don't let me go.
I'm not ready for you
to see me naked yet.
Shido?
[SHIDO] Uh huh?
[TOHKA] Will you um-- take me
out on another date sometime?
Of course.
Any time you want to.
Kids? I'd like to introduce
you to our new transfer student!
[TOHKA]
I'm Tohka Yatogami.
I'm so excited to
meet all of you!