[school bell]
Tomorrow, as in
like tomorrow?
Tomorrow! If you
have time, of course.
I thought I could
show you around town.
That sounds fun.
Wait, are you asking
me out on a date?
Uh. I guess
you can say that.
Whaddya say?
All right. I'll go
on a date with you.
That's awesome.
Is ten-thirty okay?
We can meet by
the station gates.
I'll see you there.
Looking forward to it.
Mana Takamiya supposedly
killed Kurumi Tokisaki.
We don't know why
she's still alive.
[KOTORI] Well, as long
as she is still alive,
we're sticking with the plan.
Tomorrow is a holiday,
so there's no school.
Shido, we need you to
ask Kurumi on a date.
What? Even after what
already happened?
It's because of what
already happened!
There's no guarantee
that she'll be revived
if she gets killed again.
And let's not forget
about Origami Tobiichi.
She will have told the AST.
So they'll know that
Kurumi didn't die,
which means Mana knows, as well.
Alright, then.
I understand.
I'll get her to fall
for me. I swear it.
You swear what, exactly?
[NARRATOR] Dating
everyone at the same time.
It should be paradise.
This girl, that girl,
and the girl over
there could be yours.
Unfortunately, life doesn't
always go the way we want.
[ORIGAMI] I'm going
to ask you one more time.
You're swearing what
with Kurumi Tokisaki?
[SHIDO] Uh, nothing.
I don't know what you mean.
[ORIGAMI] Just answer.
Trust me. This
is very important.
[SHIDO] Yeah, um, sorry.
Gotta go; Tohka's waiting.
I'll see ya later!
Oh, Origami.
I must say,
you look delicious, too.
[KURUMI] Yes, very delicious.
[KURUMI] But I think
I might save you for later.
Instead, I'll devour you
once I'm finished with Shido.
Oh, Shido.
[SHIDO] I'm sorry
about lunch, Tohka.
But you got a
chance to eat, right?
Yeah. I got to eat.
[TOHKA] Where is he?
Boo, we only won two
of these tickets
instead of three.
Wanna split the
cost of one more?
Oh. Hey, it's Tohka.
Why haven't
you eaten lunch yet?
Oh, no; what's wrong?
Tell us everything!
Who did what?
Shido isn't here.
And then I started
thinking about how--
Well, I started
thinking about how
we haven't really talked
that much today.
And then I uh--For some reason.
I just got sad.
Girl, you do not have
to say another word.
Shido's a jerk!
And he's taking you for granted!
That is just so lame!
No, really; he didn't
do anything wrong.
No, no, of course not.
But still, you don't
have to be sad,
and we can help!
[SHIDO] We've got
some time before dinner.
Don't you wanna go home first?
Hey, Tohka?
Are you okay?
Huh?
[SHIDO] What?
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait,
hold on a second!
I am very confused!
Okay. What's going on?
[TOHKA] Shoot,
this isn't working.
[TOHKA] What's next?
[TOHKA] Shido.
I have a question for you.
[SHIDO] Yeah?
[TOHKA] Tomorrow.
Will you go on a
date with me, please?
What? A date, huh?
[TOHKA] Pretty please?
[SHIDO] Yeah. Sure thing.
How wonderful!
Those girls were
right about everything!
Now, then.
Meet me by the statue
in front of the
station at ten a.m.!
And don't forget!
[SHIDO] What's this?
[phone buzz]
It's Origami.
Hey there, Origami.
What's up? Are you okay?
[ORIGAMI] I'm fine,
but you shouldn't be
left alone right now.
I will be waiting for
you at the fountain in front
of the station tomorrow
at exactly eleven a.m.
Wait! But I--
[ORIGAMI] Be there.
[SHIDO] Crap!
[KOTORI] Test, test.
Can you hear me?
I can't believe
you're triple booked
on such an unbelievably
important day!
You dirty little dog.
Hey, don't be mean.
Remember, you're the one
who kept me from cancelling.
[KOTORI] If you don't keep
promises you make to Tohka,
her happiness
meter will go down.
And if you cancel with Origami,
she'll be even more suspicious
than she already is.
Stop worrying.
You're not by yourself.
We'll be supporting you
with everything we've got.
All you have to do
is follow the schedule
and go with the flow.
Commander.
The plan will commence shortly.
Countdown is
beginning now.
[SHIDO] First I'm going to
the aquarium with Tohka, right?
I know you
can do it, Shido!
It's dangerous
so don't get hurt!
[SHIDO] Right.
[KOTORI] Now, let's
start our date, shall we?
[SHIIZAKI] The date has begun.
[TOHKA] Shido!
Great. She's here.
I chose her outfit.
Not too bad, huh?
You all right?
Those clothes, they um--
They look really cute.
[TOHKA] Who cares
about stupid clothes?
Can we just go now?
Sure. But do you even
know where we're going?
[KOTORI] Not the best start,
but it could've been worse.
[MINOWA] Commander, look.
[KOTORI] It's Origami.
I thought she wasn't supposed
to get here until eleven.
[REINE] Apparently,
she's impatient.
[TOHKA] So I've been wondering,
what is this aquarium thing?
Wait, you don't know?
Why'd you want to come here
if you didn't know what it was?
Don't get
the wrong idea.
I just wanted to go
out on a date with you.
It didn't matter what it was.
An aquarium's a place
that has lots of fish
and stuff that lives in water.
Really?
Do you think they'll
have fried fish?
No.
What about boiled fish?
Or poached fish?
Or steamed fish?
The only thing you ever
think about is food!
[SHIDO] You'll know
it when you see it.
[NAKATSUGAWA]
The main target has appeared.
[KOTORI] Well, at least this
one's just ten minutes early.
[TOHKA] I can't believe
this place is real!
[SHIDO] Try to use
your inside voice.
[TOHKA] Right. Sorry.
I can't help myself.
This is the neatest thing ever.
[TOHKA] Those are really
real fish out there?
[SHIDO] Yeah.
More than just fish.
[TOHKA] Wow.
It's all so beautiful.
Come with me!
I wanna go see the rest!
[KOTORI] Hey, Shido.
It's almost time for you
to meet with Kurumi.
[SHIDO] What? Already?
[KOTORI] We'll pick
you up using Fraxinus,
so go outside and find somewhere
with no one around.
Are you coming?
'Cuz you haven't moved a bit.
Ow! Oh, ow, ow!
Oh no! What's
wrong with you?
It's nothing.
Only my stomach.
I'm gonna head
to the bathroom,
keep looking at
the fish for a while.
What? But are you
going to be okay?
I need to find a place
where no one's around!
[KOTORI] Retrieval.
[KOTORI] Move him to the gates
in front of the station, now!
Hold on, already?
[SHIDO] Sorry I'm late.
[KURUMI] Don't worry.
I actually only got here
around a minute ago, myself.
So, where
shall we go first?
[SHIDO] Let me think.
[KOTORI] This is where
the real game begins.
Alright everyone!
Make your selections.
I think it should
be number two.
And then their hands can touch
during a romantic movie moment.
That would be so sweet.
Option one is the
obvious choice.
All girls' love shopping,
so he really can't go wrong.
Neither one of those
are technically bad.
Except they are both
attached to the station.
And the aquarium
is attached as well.
So the risk of running into
another girl is pretty low.
But I always say
there's no reason
to go looking for trouble.
[KOTORI] Really? So a
lingerie store is our best bet?
Well, the other day
Shido asked her
to show her panties.
She didn't seem to
have a problem with it.
[SHIDO] What?
A lingerie store, for real?
[KOTORI] Quit being
so loud, pervert!
[SHIDO] Doh!
If that's what you want.
I don't mind going
to one of those stores.
She took the bait
and ran with it!
[YOSHINO] She's so bold.
Then, let's go!
It'll be your
job to help me
choose
something cute.
[KURUMI] Wow. There's so
much here for me to try on.
Which one do you think
would look best on me?
[KOTORI] Selections, everyone!
[NAKATSUGAWA]
This is the time to attack!
Extreme flattery is sure
to reduce any
resistance to the kiss!
[KOTORI] Yeah, I mean she
was okay going to the store.
So it's probably a good call
to go for it, okay, Shido?
[gulps]
I uh-- They're
both really pretty.
But uh-- I like
that style over there.
You like the black one?
And you think it's
better than these two?
Yeah, uh, just
because, you know,
I think you'd look great in it!
Well, that's very
sweet of you to say.
I'll try it on, so
we'll know for sure.
Cool, that sounds great.
Just make it quick, okay?
[KURUMI] So how do I look?
[AI] What do you think
you're doing, Mister?
[MIKIMOTO] We have an emergency!
Why is this
loser with Kurumi?
Good question.
And what's with the lingerie?
That's so lame.
[KOTORI] Okay, Shido. It's time.
Get out of there, now.
But make sure you don't
leave Kurumi hanging.
[SHIDO] Ow!
Ow, ow, ow, my stomach.
Kurumi, I'm going
to the restroom.
I'll catch up with
you in a bit, okay?
Also, you look
in-freaking-credible!
Well.
Hey, where are you going?
Get back here, right now!
You are so lame!
[KOTORI] Make revisions
to the schedule.
Oh Shido, this is
just the beginning.
[SHIDO] Sorry. I'm late. Sorry.
[ORIGAMI] Don't worry about it.
I just got here myself.
You look kinda sleepy.
No, no,
I'm not tired at all.
So, where did, uh--
Where did you wanna go?
To the movies.
[gasps]
[SHIDO] But you don't wanna
go to the one here, right?
[ORIGAMI] Of course, silly.
We have to go to this one.
I've already picked up tickets.
[KANNAZUKI] This isn't good.
[YOSHINON]
That one's not any better.
[WAITRESS A] Okay.
I'll be back in just a bit.
Lunch?
[ORIGAMI] We have just enough
time to eat before the movie.
I figured now would be
as good a time as any.
[SHIDO] Sure. Let's eat, then.
Hey, Origami.
Why did you ask me
out on a date today?
I just didn't want
you to be by yourself.
Once the movie's over,
come back to my place.
Uh, your place. What for?
Look. You should stay
with me for a while.
I'm very serious.
[WAITRESS A] Here you go, guys!
There's something
so weird about her.
[MIKIMOTO] Commander.
It's Tohka!
[KOTORI] Aw, shoot!
[SHIDO coughs]
Want me to
Heimlich you?
[SHIDO] No thanks.
I'll be right back.
[SHIDO] Hey, Tohka!
There you are!
I was getting
really worried.
Yeah, me, too.
[stomach growls]
Do you wanna get
something to eat?
Yes, that sounds
perfect; I'm so hungry!
Man, that sure
is a lot of sushi.
'Specially after an aquarium.
More please!
Pickled mackerel!
[SHIDO] Crap.
You really bought it?
That lacy underwear?
Well, after you
told me I looked
in-freaking-credible
in it, I kinda had to.
Yeah.
[TOHKA] Shido! It's ramen!
[SHIDO] Please, stop!
[TOHKA]
Don't you understand? Ramen!
[TOHKA] Walk away!
Which room should we get?
They'll be seen!
Ow. Hey, that hurt.
I'm so sorry.
[AI] No, it's fine!
[MAI] Don't worry
about us. Are you okay?
[MII] You're so cute, it's lame.
[YOSHINON] Yeah!
Get 'em, Yoshino.
[REINE] Looks
like it's nap time.
You worked pretty hard.
[SHIDO] Sorry, Kurumi. Bathroom!
[sighs]
What is wrong
with that kid?
He's hardly making
this a stellar date.
I wonder where he keeps
rushing off to, anyway.
Oh well, it doesn't
matter, I suppose.
After all, I'm sure little Shido
will be mine soon enough.
Heh. I get warm and tingly
just thinking about it.
Not long, and then
he will be mine.
[cat meows]
[THUG A] Oh, this
guy's a feisty one.
[THUG A] Man, this is so sweet.
[THUG D] Look how close it is!
Oh, trying to get away now?
How 'bout that!
Oh, look at you.
It seems like I've
found a few boys
who are up to
something interesting.
Calm down.
Don't worry about me.
I'd like to get in on this
sweet action, if that's okay.
Believe it or not,
I've been known
to be fairly decent
with a gun, myself.
[THUG A] What should we do?
[THUG B] Heh, heh.
Have at it, sweetheart.
Wow, thanks so much
for your permission.
I certainly didn't expect
that eager welcome,
so it is appreciated.
But I have a small suggestion.
Why don't we change
the rules for fun?
It's not that complicated.
We'll just switch targets
for a little while.
Hey, what happened?
Is it broken?
Get that thing fixed!
[KOTORI] What are we missing?
Oh. I'm sorry.
No, it was my fault.
I should've been
paying attention.
It's you,
stupid Origami!
What the heck
are you doing here?
Well, stupid Tohka.
What I do is none
of your business.
That's fine.
I don't have time to waste
on a loser like
you anyway, so there.
Good, cuz neither do I.
[BOTH] Because I'm actually
on my way to find Shido.
Whatever. I'm out on
a date with Shido right now,
so you need to
stop telling lies!
You're lying!
Shido happens to
be on a date with me!
[ORIGAMI] Oh no.
This could be bad.
Who is he with right now?
Hey! Come back here.
I'm not done yelling at you yet!
[SHIDO breathes heavily]
[KOTORI] Shido, bad news.
We've lost Kurumi.
How could you lose her?
Alert! Spirit wave
reaction nearby!
[KANNAZUKI] It's in the woods
by the park's east exit.
[SHIDO screams]
[KOTORI] Shido!
Calm down! Shido!
[SHIDO retches]
[KURUMI] Oh my.
Hello, Shido.
I'm so glad you
finally decided to join us.
Help. Please.
She's a monster.
You have to help me.
Don't let her kill me!
[KURUMI] You tried
to kill something
without being ready
to be killed yourself.
Doesn't that seem odd to you?
It was helpless,
and now you are helpless.
How do you like looking
down the barrel of a gun?
Oh no, my finger
must've slipped.
[KOTORI] Shido,
get out of there!
Where do you think
you're going, Shido?
Let go of me.
Oh woe is me.
I can't believe it,
I've completely
messed things up.
I was having such
a wonderful time
on our date together,
I wanted it to last
a little longer.
Oh well. That can't
be helped now.
[MANA] Are you all
right, big brother?
[SHIDO] Mana?