[SHIDO] The Eurasian
continent was attacked
by a massive "spatial quake."
There were one hundred
fifty million victims
of this unprecedented event.
And now.
[KOTORI] Wake up!
[SHIDO]
My little sister is giving me
what could possibly be
the worst wake up call ever.
Uh... Kotori.
Darling little sister of mine.
[KOTORI] What is it?
Darling big brother of mine.
[SHIDO]
Get off of me! You're too big!
[SHIDO groans]
[KOTORI laughs]
Sorry; did that hurt?
I bet you're awake, though!
Hey!
Don't just go
right back to sleep!
Wake up!
Come on, wake up, sleepy head!
[SHIDO]
Listen to me.
Run away.
Huh?
[SHIDO]
I've contracted the mysterious
"Ten more minutes of sleep,
or else my sister goes
to Tickle Hell" virus.
Often referred to as
the T-virus for short.
What? You've got what?
[SHIDO]
Run away, Kotori!
Run, while I can
still control myself.
Wait.
But then what's gonna
happen to you, bro?
[SHIDO]
As long as you're safe,
it doesn't matter
what happens to me.
Run away!
No, I can't. I can't leave you!
[screaming]
[SHIDO laughs]
Okay, much better.
[yawning]
Huh?
[KOTORI]
I don't wanna go to tickle hell.
Someone help me.
Heh.
[screaming]
It's me. Calm down.
It's only me.
Are--Are you sure?
I am much good friend to you.
Yes. I Kotori big brother.
[sighs]
[laughs]
[MALE NEWSCASTER]
A spatial quake was recorded
early this morning near
the center of Tengu City.
There was only slight damage,
with no casualties among
residents in the area.
Investigations continue
as to the cause of
the spatial quakes...
[SHIDO]
Again? Sounded close, too.
[KOTORI] It was.
[SHIDO] Spatial quakes.
Widespread vibration phenomena.
An area randomly starts
vibrating, and no one knows why.
These quakes are
irrational, mysterious,
and unbelievably destructive.
After the massive
catastrophe thirty years ago,
spatial quakes continued
around the world
for six terrifying months.
In Japan, the Great
Southern Kantou Spatial Quake
completely flattened an area
not too far from our house.
It was total devastation.
In the twenty-five years
after that, nothing happened.
Nothing until five years
ago when a spatial quake
showed up in the
redeveloped Tengu City.
Not long after that,
we started hearing about
quakes all the time.
Most of which occurred
here, in Japan.
It's weird.
There've been a lot lately.
[KOTORI]
You're telling me.
This is happening
earlier than planned.
[SHIDO] Hold it! No sweets!
Aaahh!
Seriously?
[sighs]
Just make sure you
eat breakfast, okay?
Uh-huh!
Okay, bro! I love you!
[SHIDO] Oh, hey.
Got any requests for lunch?
Oh, yeah; one deluxe
kids plate, hooray!
Uh, that's from
a diner menu.
We don't serve that
dish at this restaurant.
C'mon. Oh, please?
Pretty please?
With a cherry on top?
It's yummy!
[KOTORI]
Deluxe Kids Plate wins!
I love eating out for lunch!
[SHIDO]
It's a diner; not that exciting.
[KOTORI] Yuhuh!
Thank you so much, bro!
Okay, so after school.
I'll be waiting for you right
here in front of the restaurant!
[SHIDO] Sounds good.
And don't break your promise!
Be here no matter
what happens!
Even if the place is taken over
by terrorists, we'll still eat!
If that goes down, I doubt
they'll let us stay.
I'll be here.
Be careful on
your way to school.
Hey, isn't that
Shido Itsuka?
Do they seem too close?
'Cause I've heard he's got
a weird sister complex.
That's so lame.
Don't forget you promised me,
so I'm gonna be
here ready to eat
even if a spatial quake happens!
[SHIDO] Sweet. Now,
go to school already!
[TONOMACHI]
Well, hey there. What's up?
Hey. Tonomachi.
You ready for the semester?
You look like you are.
Oh. Have you also heard
the rumors about him?
Yeah, he swings both
ways, as they say.
That's so lame.
Are you okay, Ai?
I'm perfect.
I just saw "Super
Genius" creepin'.
That's so lame.
[TONOMACHI]
Nice coincidence, huh, Shido?
Lucky you being put in the
same class with me again.
Some people would
call this fate.
I would be one of those people.
Of course you would.
[cell phone chimes]
Hold on. 'Cuse me. It's my girl.
What? Girl like girl friend?
Oh yeah, you wanna
meet her? Check it out.
[SHIDO]
That's a dating sim!
[TONOMACHI]
Yeah, so what?
Doesn't change the fact
that she's my girlfriend.
Don't judge me;
a dating sim will tell you
everything you need to know
about how to treat women.
It's like a textbook for lovin'.
This particular app is
groovy because she--
[ORIGAMI]
Shido Itsuka.
[SHIDO] Who? Me?
Yes.
[SHIDO]
How do you know my name?
You mean you don't remember?
Hey. Who is she?
Am I supposed to know her?
Of course you are.
That's Origami Tobiichi,
otherwise known as
the "Super Genius."
For real? Crazy.
She knows me?
[TONOMACHI]
That chick always has
some of the best
grades in our class.
She's ridiculous at sports,
and I mean, look at her.
Gorgeous.
On my "Girls I Probably Ought
To Have As A Girlfriend List,"
she's never been out of
the top three. Like ever.
How do you not know one of the
most popular kids in our school?
But more importantly,
why in the world does
Origami know who you are?
I wish I knew,
but I have no idea.
[bell rings]
[TONOMACHI]
Oh heck yeah! It's Tamae!
It's Miss Okamine, please!
Now quiet down.
I'll be your homeroom
teacher this year.
I hope you guys
are ready to learn!
[applause]
[SHIDO]
Origami Tobiichi.
Why does she know who I am?
And why is she looking at me?
So weird.
What the heck is going on?
[bell rings]
[TONOMACHI] Hey Shido.
Wanna go home together?
[SHIDO]
Sorry. I've got plans.
Oh, yeah? Is it a girl?
[SHIDO]
Technically.
It's just Kotori, though.
Oh, I understand.
Besides, as far as I know,
there's not a girl
in this school
with a sensitive and kind enough
spirit to have lunch with you.
Thanks, but that
was not a compliment.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Your attention, please.
This is not a drill.
A spatial quake!
Another one?
[SHIDO]
We need to evacuate.
The shelter near the school
should be safe enough.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
I repeat,
there have been
precursory signs...
[SHIDO]
Where's she going?
[KAWAGOE] Contriella aura
avu yutorimme skalv.
[SHIIZAKI] Intensitetto folto
shigelsa tori conma fein.
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Monsto matchinihi Princess!
[KANNAZUKI]
Ah... She's here.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] I repeat.
There have been precursory signs
of an impending spatial
quake in this vicinity.
Please evacuate to the
nearest shelter immediately.
This is not a drill.
I repeat. There have
been precursory signs
of an impending spatial
quake in this vicinity.
Please evacuate to the
nearest shelter immediately.
Ah! Everyone please calm down!
And don't forget your three D's.
Don't push, don't run,
don't walk-- wait.
You might wanna take
it down a scosche.
Of course.
You're right. I'm sorry.
[SHIDO] I hope Kotori is
evacuating like she should.
Surely she's not still gonna
try to meet me at the diner.
[KOTORI] I'll be here even
if a spatial quake happens!
[SHIDO] Come on.
Please don't be waiting
in front of that diner.
She has to have
gone to a shelter.
She's fine. She's gotta be fine.
I bet the shelter she's
in just has bad reception
or she has her phone
on silent or something.
Let me check her location.
Just in case.
No!
Hey. Wait! Shido!
[KOTORI]
Okay, bro! I love you!
[SHIDO] Why?
[KOTORI]
Thank you so much, bro!
[SHIDO] Why?
Why did she not
just take shelter?
The city's about
to be destroyed,
and she's worried
about a promise?
Kotori! Kotori! Kotori!
[rumbling]
Ahh!
Whoa-- What was that?
[SHIDO] It's a girl.
What's she doing?
[GIRL]
Not you, too.
I see.
So it's true.
You came here to kill me.
Do not try denying you
are here to kill me.
I must deal with you
before the others arrive.
Wait!
Just wait! Please!
That's--that's not
why I came here!
What?
I-- I could never kill anybody.
Is that what you're here for?
[SHIDO screams]
Why do they not realize the
futility of their attacks?
[SHIDO]
This isn't just any girl.
If she's that strong,
why does she look so sad?
[yelling]
[SHIDO]
Tobiichi? Is that you?
Shido, it's you.
[SHIDO] Why are you
wearing those clothes?
[SHIDO yells]
[KASHIWAZAKI]
Coordinates FJ-eighteen-twenty.
The target, "Princess,"
has been lost.
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Area reaction waves
below detection threshold.
[SHIDO] Hello?
[VOICE] Finally.
We meet again.
[SHIDO]
Who are you?
[VOICE]
I'm so glad.
But just wait.
Just a little while longer.
I won't ever let you go again.
I won't ever be wrong again.
Soon.
[GIRL] Hmm...
It appears you're awake now.
Wait, I don't know
you. Who are you?
My name is Reine Murasame.
Just call me Reine.
I'm the Head Analyst here.
There's no reason
for you to freak out.
First Aid is hardly
out of my league.
[SHIDO]
That supposed to be reassuring?
So, here's a question.
Where exactly am I?
You're resting in
Fraxinus's sickbay.
You were unconscious,
so it was decided this was
the best course of action.
Fraxina-what-now?
Did I pass out?
Oh, right. I ended up in the
middle of that chick fight.
Wait, Kotori!
But my sister! I need
to go find my sister!
She's waiting for me
in front of the diner!
She could be--
What you need is to calm down.
Your sister is perfectly fine.
[SHIDO]
What? She is?
I'm assuming you want some
sort of explanation now?
Apologies, but that
isn't really my forte.
You should ask the Vice
Commander for more details.
I've brought him with me.
[KANNAZUKI] Thank you
for taking care of him.
It's very nice to meet you.
My name is Kyohei Kannazuki
and I am the Vice Commander.
Welcome, Shido.
We're glad you're here.
[gasps]
[SHIDO] Kotori?
Glad you could make it, bro!
Like the idiot said,
welcome to Ratatoskr.
[MALE MECHANIC]
Penetration angle, check.
A.N.S, set.
[ORIGAMI]
Release connection.
[RYOKO]
I got you.
Good work.
[ORIGAMI]
Captain Kusabe.
You're working
yourself too hard.
Take it easy, okay?
[KOTORI] This thing is a
monster called a "Spirit."
It was lost not long ago.
That means it disappeared.
And this is what we call--
[SHIDO] Wait! Will you
shut up for a second?
Don't be rude.
The commander is
taking the time
to explain everything
to you personally.
You should be on your
knees bowing in gratitude.
If you want, I certainly
wouldn't mind letting you
lick my boots while
you're down there.
What? Really, I can?
[KANNAZUKI groans]
Oh, yeah. Thank you
for that, Commander.
And uh-- you are Kotori?
[KOTORI]
Of course.
Have you forgotten what
my face looks like, Shido?
No bro?
[KOTORI] I knew your memory was
bad, but not Alzheimer's bad.
Well, I guess we'll
have to admit you
to a nursing home pretty soon.
So, uh. What's going
on? Where are we?
Quit freaking.
I'll explain the specifics
to you later, but first.
You need to remember the three
things I'm about to say.
One, that girl is a "Spirit."
She doesn't belong
in this world,
and simply appearing
on our planet
causes everything
around her to blow up
whether she wants it to or not.
Blow up? Why?
[KOTORI]
You are so dumb.
You know those things
we call "Spatial Quakes"?
Well, Spirits just like
that girl down there
are the ones responsible
for making them happen.
[SHIDO gasps]
[SHIDO] How could
one girl do all that?
Ready for two?
These are the ground
force's Anti-Spirits Team.
When a Spirit appears,
the AST fly to their location
and take care of it.
Meaning, they kill them.
What? Kill them?
It's true.
You came here to
kill me, didn't you?
And now for three.
There is another way to
deal with these Spirits
without having to
rely on the AST.
This is the reason you're here
and where your help
will be most needed.
Me? Help how?
We'll have to make sure you
start training tomorrow.
I'll leave the rest
of the details
up to the person in charge
of your development--
in the meantime, just go
back to school like normal.
Wait! Will you slow down?
Why would you train me?
I mean, seriously,
what could I possibly do?
[KANNAZUKI screams]
No one is asking your
opinion on the matter.
--Your only option is 'yes'.
--But.
[KOTORI]
Now I have a question.
What were you doing
down there, Shido?
Did you want to die?
[SHIDO] No, stupid!
I was looking for you!
Remember, you said
you'd be at the diner
even if there was a quake!
[KOTORI] I said that,
but how was I supposed to know
you'd follow through?
Look, Kotori. Besides
being dependable,
your phone's locator
showed me you were there!
You don't say?
Oh, yeah--I guess
that does make sense.
Although, technically
we're above the diner.
Huh?
Disable the filter.
[gasps]
We're currently fifteen thousand
meters above Tengu City.
You're onboard an
airship called Fraxinus.
[TAMAE] Is everyone enjoying
day two of the new semester?
Well, I am because today we have
a brand new assistant
homeroom teacher with us!
I'm Reine Murasame.
And I'm excited to be here.
Ahh!
[SHIDO] How did you get
to be one of my teachers?
Tell me what's going on!
Please, Miss Murasame.
[REINE]
You can just call me Reine.
'Kay, Shin?
[SHIDO]
My name is Shido.
Is that right? Wow.
Sorry Shin. My bad.
You can't be
serious! Come on!
You didn't even
try getting it right!
It's more convenient for
me to keep close to you
if I'm a member of the
school's teaching staff.
And you should have been able
to figure that much
out on your own.
Try not to be so stupid!
Hey, why don't you tell
me why you're even here?
Don't you have school?
[KOTORI] I got
permission to come today.
Fine.
So are you finally
gonna explain to me
what this training
is for, or what?
It'll start to
make more sense
once you start using
the training software.
Hit it, Reine!
[SHIDO] Huh?
This is a dating sim.
Tonomachi was playing it.
Um, no it's not.
Take another look.
[SHIDO]
My Little... Shido?
[ORIGAMI]
So, Shido.
About yesterday.
[SHIDO] Uh huh.
Please, just keep
that to yourself.
In fact, it would
be for the best
if you forgot about everything
you saw yesterday.
Would it?
You mean that girl, right?
Look, Tobiichi.
I, um.
I think she's might be--
She's a spirit.
That thing is an enemy
that I must defeat.
Why?
You really think
they're so evil?
Spirits killed my parents.
They burned them.
They are very evil.
And they will pay.