[MANA] That was
pretty close, Shido.
Are you okay?
[SHIDO] Mana? I--
Right.
This is probably a
little shocking, huh?
[KURUMI] Excuse me.
But we were in the
middle of a lovely date,
and I find it terribly rude of
you to interrupt us like this.
Gimmie just a
minute, big brother.
This won't take very long.
Kurumi!
[SHIDO] Stop it! Don't kill her!
I knew it. You really
are good, Shido.
Mana. Why?
[SHIDO] How can you stand
there like nothing happened?
You just killed a person.
[MANA] I just killed a Spirit.
Besides, I do this all the time.
[NARRATOR] "It" is something
all things are given.
It cannot be bought,
and it cannot be sold.
People often waste it, hold
it dear, and chase after it.
If only we knew what "it" was.
[MANA] It seems you've
already heard a few things
from Master Sergeant Tobiichi.
Well, you should
probably pretend
this was all a bad dream.
Just forget it ever happened.
How could I forget it?
She won't stay dead.
Kurumi Tokisaki, or
"Nightmare" is a special Spirit.
No matter how many
times she's killed,
or how she's killed,
this Spirit appears again
and kills more people,
as if she's on a
mission for murder.
So, I kill her
over and over again.
And I will continue to kill her.
Over and over and over--.
[SHIDO] Will you shut up!
Please, don't tell me
you're used to killing.
I don't want to hear
you talk like that.
[MANA] This job is one
that can only be done by me.
[SHIDO] Mana, wait!
Damn it!
[cat meows]
Mana. Why?
I don't know. Why?
[KOTORI]
The plan's been aborted.
We'll pick you up with Fraxinus.
Shido, can you hear me?
[TOHKA] Shido!
What happened?
We've been looking for you.
Spill it.
What's going on?
[TOHKA] Oh no, you've been hurt!
I'm so sorry.
Did I make it worse?
No. Uh-- Sorry.
[TOHKA and ORIGAMI]
Shido!
[SHIDO] Hey.
Hey. Is your arm
feeling any better?
[SHIDO] Yeah.
Good. We can go, then!
Wait, go where exactly?
[TOHKA] We're
continuing our date, silly.
[TOHKA] Can I have
some bread, please?
Corn dogs! Steamed
pork buns! Here.
Thanks. That was sweet.
Come on, let's go!
Hold on!
Tohka. I don't have
much money on me.
Don't worry about money.
Reine let me borrow
her magic buy things card!
You mean credit card?
[TOHKA] She also
told me about you.
And Kurumi and Mana.
[SHIDO] I see.
Then, you know
I have to stop Kurumi
from killing more people.
[TOHKA] Yeah.
[SHIDO] I'm just-- I'm not sure
how I should go
about it with her.
I mean, Kurumi's a Spirit,
but she's different
from you or Yoshino.
Now that isn't true
at all, and you know it.
Kurumi and I are
the same. We are.
Remember that I
had you here for me.
You saved me.
I didn't even know
I needed you, but I did.
Then, you asked me out
on a date, like today,
and showed me how amazing
and beautiful this
world really is.
If it weren't
for you, Shido,
I most likely would have
ended up just like Kurumi.
There's only one difference
between the two of us.
And that--
--is having someone close
who's reaching out his hand.
Tohka. Thank you.
You've helped me
realize what's important.
Yeah?
Does that mean
you aren't scared?
No, not quite.
Don't worry.
I'll be here to protect you.
Well, thanks, that
makes me feel better.
I know, right?
Shido, can we stay like
this for a while longer?
[SHIDO] Sure.
[KURUMI] Well,
good morning, Shido.
How are you today?
I'm fine.
You are so dead, dude.
How dare you show
your face around here!
That is, I dunno, lame!
[TOHKA] Hold it!
Please, leave Shido alone.
Let's just go this way.
[KURUMI] I have to admit,
I'm a little surprised.
I thought for sure you wouldn't
want to come to school today,
you know, after all
that crazy drama.
[SHIDO] Kurumi.
That's me.
So you know,
I've made the decision
that I need to save you.
Well, that's kind of
a strange thing to say.
I will not let you
kill anyone else.
I will also not
let Mana kill you.
How very big of you.
Little Shido.
I've made the decision
I need to test you
and see if you're really
telling me the truth.
[MANA] Ratatoskr, huh?
I can't believe you
and my big brother
are a part of that
twisted organization.
I'm surprised you
found that out.
Now, what do you want?
It's about Shido.
You're negligent, at best.
How could you send him unarmed
to go meet with
dangerous Spirits?
You're a failure
as a little sister.
So I'm going to take over
that role from now on.
Oh, you have
gotta be kidding me.
And let a corrupt company
like Deus Ex Machina
get their hands on him?
I don't think so, Mana.
How did you know?
You should stop
underestimating me.
I know that except
for Ratatoskr,
your little group supplies
all the military forces
around the world with Realizers.
And you, you're one
of their employees
who was sent to the AST.
[bell rings]
[sighs]
Here goes!
[REINE] Kurumi has not been seen
leaving the school as of yet.
Still though, our real
problem is whether or not
she'll listen to
what we have to say.
Hey, where's Kotori?
Something just came up.
She'll be back soon,
but this time I'll have
to be your Navigator.
Okay, got it.
Let's do this.
[SHIDO] What happened? Reine!
We're analyzing right now.
I'm not going to stand here
and listen to you
call us corrupt.
You know nothing about DEM.
That place gave me a reason to
live after I lost my memory.
I can't thank them
enough for their help.
Really?
Even after what
they did to you?
What are you
talking about?
I've discovered
something terrible
from Mana Takamiya's cup.
What they've
done is wrong.
Her body has been implanted
with far too much magical power.
Sadly, she's not likely to
live more than ten years.
You don't know?
They haven't told you?
[cell phone rings]
It's Kotori.
What's up?
[KANNAZUKI] Commander,
there's an intense
Spirit wave reaction
at Shido's High School.
It's coming from
Kurumi Tokisaki.
[KOTORI] Understood.
[REINE] It's a
wide area barrier.
The kind of barrier meant
to debilitate everyone
within its range.
She did this. But why?
[TOHKA] Hey, Shido.
[SHIDO] Tohka!
Are you all right?
Well, my body feels
heavy for some reason.
Why am I the only one
who's not affected?
[REINE] Since you've
sealed the powers
of both Tohka and Yoshino,
it's like you've received
their divine protection.
Given these conditions,
you're the only one
who can move normally.
[KURUMI] Shido, darling.
Can you hear me?
If you need anything at all,
feel free to join
me on the roof.
Something tells
me you might want
to get here as soon
as possible, though.
[KURUMI laughs]
Listen to me.
Stay right here, okay?
And don't worry!
I'm going to save her!
Be careful, Shido!
[ORIGAMI] Identifying AST,
Origami Tobiichi.
One basic Realizer.
Activate at once.
[KURUMI] Welcome, Shido.
I'm glad you were so
eager to come see me.
[RYOKO] I'm showing you're
using the emergency uniform.
What's going on?
[ORIGAMI] Dangerous
situation. I need support.
Hello, Origami.
You seem like you're in a rush.
Where might you be off to?
[ORIGAMI] I'm here to
protect Shido from you.
No, that doesn't
work for me.
Terribly sorry, but you'll
have to stay right here.
Oh, Shido. Don't go.
It's not safe to go
up there alone. Shido!
Come on. Get up. Move!
There you go, Tohka.
I can do it!
[gunshot]
Hey! Who did that?
Kurumi?
Good morning, Tohka.
Going anywhere?
Kurumi. What is
all of this about?
Isn't it pretty?
My Time-Eating Castle?
This barrier sucks up the time
from anyone who
steps on my shadow.
The time?
Your eye's a clock.
That's right;
what you're looking
at is my time.
Lovely thing.
I suppose you could
call it my life span.
My Angel has such
a wonderful power,
but unfortunately, it
does have that nasty habit
of eating up my time
whenever I use it.
So, I have to replenish it
with other peoples' time
every once in a while.
What?
Other peoples' time?
[KURUMI] Everyone is
my pitiful, adorable prey.
But you, you're
special, Shido,
and you don't even
realize it. Guess what.
You're the reason I'm here.
I came all this way just
so I could become one
with you in person
and see the look
on your face when I eat you.
Okay, fine.
I'm the one you want.
So don't hurt everyone else!
I'll think about
that option,
but first, I want
you to take back
what you said this morning.
Obviously, you're not going
to "save" me now, are you?
Come on, Shido.
Don't you think
I'm downright awful
to cause all this pain
for such a silly reason?
You can say it.
You hate me,
and it's clear to you
that I'm not someone
who deserves mercy.
I will eat you,
but first I'm giving you
the chance to take
your words back.
Do that, darling,
and I'll reward you
by taking down this barrier
so those people won't die.
[SHIDO gasps]
[KURUMI laughs]
So what will it be, Shido?
Better make your
decision quickly,
or there will be nothing
left for you to save.
Take down the
barrier, Kurumi.
Do it. But I will
not give up on you.
Why are
you so stubborn?
[KURUMI sighs]
Your choices confuse me.
[alarm sounds]
[KURUMI] You know
what that sound means,
so what could
I possibly be doing?
It's the spatial
quake alarm!
[alrm bells]
A quake?
She can't, can she?
She's causing a spatial
quake on purpose.
We didn't know any
Spirit could do that.
[KURUMI laughs]
What is my little
Shido going to do?
If a spatial
quake occurs now,
what do you imagine will happen
to all those
unconscious students?
Shin.
Kurumi's emotional condition
has started changing.
It's seems almost as if
she's frightened of you.
That's it! Listen!
You've been saying you came here
just so you could eat me, right?
If that's true, stop the quake!
If you don't stop it...
...I'll jump off this
roof and kill myself.
You're making
yourself a hostage?
Nice threat,
but something tells me
you're not gonna
follow through with it.
Watch me.
[SHIDO winces]
[KURUMI] Are you kidding me?
Damn it. That was
incredibly stupid!
I'm not as stupid
as you think,
because now I know I have
worth to you as a hostage.
If you could go ahead and stop
the spatial quake,
that'd be great.
Oh, and take down the barrier
while you're at it.
If you refuse, I swear
I'll kill myself.
This is ridiculous.
[snaps]
Oh, there is
one more thing.
How much more
can there be?
[SHIDO] I want you to allow
yourself to have another chance.
Are we back to this?
Trust me, I'm more
trouble than I'm worth.
That isn't true,
even for you.
Listen to me.
You can change and be happy
if you want, and I know you do.
I know it.
If that wasn't an option,
you wouldn't have had
so much fun on our date.
You're wrong.
It's too late.
It's not too late.
I can help you!
Yes, you'll have to live
with what you've done
for the rest of your life.
But still, Kurumi, it doesn't
matter how terrible you've been.
Nothing will ever give me
a reason not to save you.
What? I--
I don't know.
Why are you so kind?
Am I worth it? Can I--
[squelching sounds]
[KURUMI B] It doesn't
really work for us
to have you fall for his
pretty words, you know.
[SHIDO gasps]
I-- Thank you
so much, Shido.
[KURUMI B] Well, that's that.
Why don't you go
take a rest now?
[KURUMI B] Goodness, me!
[SHIDO] What? Kurumi? But how?
[KURUMI B] It seems
the me I chose
for this endeavor might have
been a little too young.
Now, why don't we put a stop
to this tediousness, already?
[SHIDO] Mana!
Hi. Are you ever not
in trouble, big brother?
[KURUMI B laughs]
[KURUMI B]
Right on time, like usual.
You've always had
the strange ability
to cut my Spirit
armor so easily.
This time, though.
Things have changed,
so you might as well accept
that I won't die
and you won't live.
Hear me, Zaphkiel.
Come to me, now!
Daletto!
Your talent for
healing is impressive.
[KURUMI B laughs]
I'm not healing
in the least.
I'm simply turning
back the clock.
Come. Fight.
Let the fun begin!
Sure, bring it on!
I'll just kill you
like a normally do.
[laughs]
[KURUMI B] You still
don't get it, do you?
Try as much as you like,
but there's no way
you'll ever be able
to get rid of me completely!
We'll see about that.
Get ready to die!
[KURUMI B] Aleph!
[SHIDO] Mana!
[MANA] Ahh!
Zayin!
But how?
Mana, no!
[gunshots]
[SHIDO] Kurumi?
She's alive!
[MANA] Please,
don't come any closer.
[TOHKA and ORIGAMI]
Shido!
[SHIDO] You're here!
Oh, how sweet. Looks
like everyone made it!
Kurumi.
You're gonna pay for
what you're doing here!
You can't run from us.
Wow; I'm positively terrified.
To attack poor little Kurumi
with so many people all at once.
Lucky for me, though.
I'm playing for keeps today.
[KURUMI B]
Isn't that right, ladies?
[SHIDO] What the
hell is all this?
[KURUMI B] This is
my past, my dear Shido.
My history. They're
beautiful, aren't they?
Now do you understand why
I can never fully be killed?
Where did they
all come from?
Time. Now, we need
to finish this.
[KURUMI B laughs]
[KURUMI B] After you're
gone, I can be free.
There you go.
You should really stop getting
your hopes up for me, Shido.
I've taken some precautions
to make sure you
can't seduce me again.
[alarm sounds]
[SHIDO] No! You can't!
Prepare to be surrounded
by so much death,
the last thing you'll
want to save is me.
Please, no!
[KURUMI B laughs maniacally]
What is the
meaning of this?
You mean you didn't know?
Surprise, surprise.
Spatial quakes
can be neutralized
if they run into a tremor
of equal force at the onset.
[ORIGAMI] It's her.
What? Sis?
Don't let me forget to give
this back to you, Shido.
Burn, Camael!
Bro. What do you say?
Are you about ready
to begin our date?