I don't want to go just yet!
Before the shuttle launches
and I leave this world,
there's something I think
you outta know about me.
[SHIDO]
What is it, Ririko?
Everyone wants you to get really
good at flirting with Spirits
so you can make them
fall in love with you.
And you're supposed to get
better by practicing on me.
[SHIDO]
Yeah, that's the plan.
What about it?
[RIRIKO]
Oh, it's just that I'm afraid.
I'm afraid-- I might be
falling in love with you.
It's true.
We've known each other forever
and you've always treated
me like a little sister,
but do you think you
can start looking at me
as a woman instead?
This is the best day ever!
Don't you worry about a thing.
I'll even wave to
you from Jupiter,
it's not super far away!
Until next time, big brother!
[SHIDO] All right! Ha, ha!
I rock!
[NARRATOR] Spirits.
Mysterious girls appearing
from another world.
Should we fight against
their pure strength
with weapons of war,
or should we address
them with love?
Now, mankind is faced with
the ultimate decision.
[YOUNG ORIGAMI]
Dad! Mom!
Origami!
Shin.
[SHIDO]
Uh, yes, Reine?
[KOTORI]
Are you daydreaming again?
It's time to implement
Stage 2 of your training,
so you better be ready.
[SHIDO] Huh?
This is training?
Good afternoon, Shido.
Is there something
I can help you with?
No, thank you.
[KOTORI]
What do you think you're doing?
Quit wasting everyone's time.
Hurry up and make her
fall in love with you.
[SHIDO]
Do I have to?
You ought to know by now
that seducing a Spirit
is easier said than done.
If you can't even
make a human love you,
how do you expect to
convince a Spirit to?
You're asking the wrong guy,
I'm not a stud.
[KOTORI] We know!
Just throw out a few compliments
and see what happens.
If she responds well, we'll
give you further instructions.
Um. Is there something
on your mind?
[SHIDO] Miss Okamine, that's
a cute outfit you're wearing!
What? Goodness, you
really think so?
Oh my, that is very
flattering of you.
Oh, yes! It really
does look good!
So does your hair!
And those sexy glasses!
Perfect shoes!
Perfect stockings!
Perfect attendance book! Heh.
Shido? Is everything all right?
[KOTORI] You got way too
into that. Stop being creepy!
[TAMAE] I'm kind of busy right
now, so I'll see you in class.
[SHIDO stammers]
[REINE]
This can be fixed.
All right.
Listen closely and
do exactly as I say.
[sighs]
Here's the truth.
I love homeroom.
I look forward to
going to it every day.
Well that's nice to hear!
I'm so glad that you like it.
[SHIDO]
The main reason is because
I get to see you all the time.
I can't help it.
I think I've fallen
in love with you.
Come on, don't say
such silly things!
Honestly, I'm flattered,
but students and teachers
can't love each other!
No. Don't tell me that.
I'm dead serious.
I want to marry you!
[TAMAE]
You want to marry me?
Is it true?
Once you're old enough to get
married, I'll be in my thirties.
Is that ok? You need
to meet my parents!
Daddy gets so protective
but I think he'll like you!
He might even give us the house!
Once you graduate
and get a decent job
I can retire and
start having babies!
Huh. We underestimated
the enthusiasm
of 29-year old single women.
They make for easy targets.
It'll be annoying if she gets
more involved than necessary.
Hey Shido, we're done here,
so make up some excuses and
get out of there pronto.
I'm really sorry Miss Okamine,
I don't think I'm ready for
that level of commitment!
We can start out in an
apartment and work our way up
to a three-bedroom
condo with a backyard!
And don't worry about
wedding planning!
I've been saving up
for fifteen years!
You can take care of
the DJ, I'll do the rest!
Let's wait till Valentines Day,
that'd make it extra special!
[KOTORI] You've found a
market with older women.
Good to know.
[SHIDO] Shut up!
How can you be so calm
when I'm about to-- Ahh!
Oh man. I'm sorry 'bout that.
I'm alright.
[KOTORI]
Perfect timing!
Why don't you practice
with her, too?
[SHIDO] Huh?!
[KOTORI] She's around
the same age as you,
so it'll be natural.
Plus, even though
she's not a Spirit,
she's a member of the AST.
Doesn't seem like the type
to spread rumors either.
Spread rumors
about what?
[KOTORI]
Just talk to her already!
[SHIDO] Ugh.
Uh... Hey Tobiichi!
Those clothes look nice on you!
Where'd you get 'em?
[ORIGAMI]
It's a uniform.
Come on, idiot, you have to
put in more effort than that.
Again, with more feeling!
[SHIDO]
I don't know how.
[REINE]
Shin, follow my lead.
To be honest,
I already know.
I've known all about you
for quite a while now.
I'm aware of that.
Oh, is that so? Nice.
I'm real glad we're in the
same class this semester.
In fact I watch you all the time
during class when you study.
Yes, likewise.
Is that so? How random.
I also like sneaking into
your locker after school
to sniff your gym clothes.
Same here.
Okay. I wasn't expecting that.
And why not?
Who knew we'd have
so much in common.
So do you want
to go out with me?
That came out of nowhere!
Don't you think this
is a little sudden?
I wouldn't mind.
I wouldn't mind
going out with you.
[SHIDO]
Uh... Cool.
So you wanna, like, go somewhere
with me, something like that?
[ORIGAMI]
Like a movie?
I'm sorry, I assumed you were
asking me out on a date, Shido.
Am I wrong?
No, not at all, that's
exactly what I meant.
[ORIGAMI] Good.
[SHIDO] Dang it.
That's exactly what I meant?
How come Reine didn't bail me
out of that one? I'm screwed!
Uh... What's this?
[ORIGAMI] For you,
because you like my uniform.
[alarm sounds]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Your attention, please.
This is not a drill.
There have been precursory signs
of an impending spatial
quake in this vicinity.
Please evacuate...
[ORIGAMI]
Something just came up. Bye.
Hey! Wait a second!
Where are you going?
[KOTORI] A spatial quake
is about to happen.
Head back to the
Fraxinus for now.
[SHIDO]
Do you think it's a Spirit?
Yes. Princess.
She'll be appearing
at your exact location.
Raizen High School.
[indistinct speaking
over intercom]
[alarm sounds]
They're on their way, now.
Roger that.
[FEMALE AST SOLDIER]
Here we go.
The quake has started.
[crumbling sounds]
[KOTORI] Consider
yourself lucky, Shido.
The AST's CR-units are deadly,
but they weren't built
for indoor combat.
As long as Princess
remains inside the school,
the AST will have a hard time
interfering with
whatever you do.
[SHIDO]
With what I do?
You know exactly what
I'm talking about.
Relax, this is what you've been
training for the past week.
You're as ready
as you'll ever be.
You want to save the Spirit.
Or am I wrong?
[SHIDO] She's right.
I don't ever want to see that
sad look on her face again.
Kotori. You're absolutely
sure I can do this?
[KOTORI] Yes. Just
believe in yourself.
You represent a different way
of dealing with the Spirits,
a more intimate method.
Remember that.
Be friendly with them, use sweet
talk, and make them fall for me.
You're gonna do just fine.
Besides, the Fraxinus
has got your back.
Behold the pride of Ratatoskr,
ready to respond to
any circumstance!
With five marriages and five
divorces under his belt,
the Love Master.
"Bad Marriage" Kawagoe!
Hey there!
[KOTORI] It's the working girl's
favorite midnight client,
CEO Mikimoto!
Who doesn't love love?
[KOTORI] Go after this lady's
fella and you'll regret it!
Don't you dare piss her off.
"Nail Knocker" Shiizaki!
The man with no fewer
than a hundred wives.
"Dimension Breaker" Nakatsugawa!
A-okay!
[KOTORI] Lastly, a woman
whose love is so strong,
not even a silly restraining
order can keep her away.
"Deep Love" Minowa!
Fantastic,
I'm relying on perverts.
[REINE] Don't worry, everyone
is good at what they do.
And that's only a portion
of the troops on our side!
Just stay calm.
Even if you die once,
you can always start a new
game without a penalty.
[SHIDO] I'm pretty sure
this isn't a game.
[KOTORI] Have faith
in your little sister!
Now get in there and flirt!
[gasps]
[SHIDO] Ahh!
[SHIDO coughs]
Wait just a minute!
I don't want to fight with you!
Please, listen to me.
[PRINCESS]
What's your name?
And why are you following me?
Because--
[KOTORI]
Don't answer yet!
[MINOWA]
There has been a change
in the mental state
of the Spirit.
[KAWAGOE]
Reaction analysis complete.
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Displaying choices onscreen.
[SHIDO]
My name is Shido Itsuka.
I've come to save you!
I'm just a passerby.
Please don't kill me!
Before asking someone's name,
you should give your own.
[KOTORI]
Well, there they are.
Now everyone get to work!
[KOTORI]
No surprise here.
You guys went with
the same one I did.
The first choice is a
tried and true classic,
but it doesn't apply
in the situation.
And it does sound
a little cliché.
Option two is also out.
If he escapes, he can't
continue the conversation.
Number three it is.
I agree.
In this case, three
makes the most sense.
She'll let him live and
he'll get to know her better.
'Kay, Shido, we've
made up your mind!
Now listen closely and
then repeat after me.
[PRINCESS]
What are you waiting for?
Answer the question already!
Before asking for
someone's name,
you should really
give your own first!
I hate you, Kotori!
[KOTORI] Well,
that was unexpected!
Unexpected my ass,
I could've been dead!
No more time for games.
If you do not answer me,
I can only assume
you are my enemy.
[SHIDO]
My name is Shido Itsuka.
I'm a student at this school.
I've got no reason to fight you.
Hold on.
This isn't the first time
we've crossed paths.
No, it's not.
I saw you on the
tenth in the city.
That's right. I thought so.
I remember you saying
something odd to me that day.
[SHIDO winces]
You said you didn't
come to kill me,
and that you couldn't
kill anyone.
And now I know that was a lie.
Why else would you be here?
Your face. How come
you always look so sad?
I'm not trying to do anything.
And it's true. I really
have no reason to kill you.
[PRINCESS] Quit lying!
Every single human
is out to get me.
I haven't done a thing to
them yet they want me dead.
I swear, that's not true!
You never answered me.
You claim to have no
intention of killing anyone.
If that's really the truth,
tell my why it is you came here.
Her first reaction
wasn't all that pretty.
This time, option one's
probably the safest choice.
[SHIDO]
I-- I wanted to meet you!
To meet me?
Why would you want that?
[KOTORI]
Do you guys have any ideas?
[KAWAGOE] I recommend a
straightforward approach.
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Yeah, be clear and direct!
This girl's way too dense
to get anything subtle.
[KOTORI]
That's a good point.
We've already wasted enough time
answering all of
these questions.
Um. It's simple.
I came here because
I'm interested in you.
I'm in no mood to joke around.
I know, and neither am I.
You want to know the truth?
I came here so I
could talk to you.
I don't even care
what we talk about.
Not one bit!
You can ignore me
if you want to!
But know this, I'm not
like every other human.
Because--
[KOTORI] Stop it,
wait for our signal!
Because I'll never
let you down!
[PRINCESS] You said your
name was Shido, right?
And when you said you
were interested in me,
were you being serious?
[SHIDO]
Yes, I was.
But like
serious serious?
[SHIDO]
Serious serious.
[PRINCESS] One-hundred
percent serious serious?
[SHIDO] One-thousand
percent serious serious!
Jerk!
Who would seriously fall
for your amateur tricks?
Stupid, dummy!
But that was
from the heart!
Then again, this is different.
I still don't know what
your intentions are.
But you are the only
human I've ever had
a normal conversation with.
You know this world,
which could serve me well.
It might just work.
Yep, it's settled.
This should prove
your usefulness.
Uh, thanks I guess.
Um. Oh yeah, what was
your name again?
My name? I've never
had one of those.
But I suppose I will need
one if I want to find out
why humans are so awful.
Okay. Why don't you come up
with something you can call me?
Well she's certainly putting
the Fraxinus to work, isn't she?
All right crew, we need to
think of a name, on the double!
The few suggestions we have
aren't gonna be enough.
Do you want to call in the
troops from around the world?
One step ahead of you!
[phone beeps]
Gosh, now what does she want?
Heh, heh, heh.
Your wish is my command,
my digital darling!
Isn't that that
fool Tonomachi?
He's probably sending
a dirty text to Shido!
That's so lame.
Come on man, we're
not naming Princess
after one of your ex-wives!
I don't even know how to
pronounce that gibberish!
[MIKIMOTO]
It's Clare-ah-bell.
[KOTORI]
The nineteen twenties are over!
Can't anyone here think of
a halfway decent girl's name?
What about Tome?
Tome!
Tome sounds kinda neat, right?
Wow, she's mad.
Was Tome that bad?
Don't think I can't
tell when a human
is attempting to make
fun of me. You got it?
[SHIDO]
Okay, just a minute!
Apologies to anyone named Tome,
but I don't think
I know a single girl
that would like that name.
Think, Shido!
There has to be a
perfect name for her!
How about Tohka?
Tohka. Yeah,
I guess that'll work.
Is this how it's written?
It is.
[TOHKA] Huh...
Tohka.
Now I have a name!
I think I like it.
Thank you.
Yeah. Yeah, you're welcome.
Tohka just means "tenth,"
as in the day we met.
But hey, it's not like
she'll ever need to know that.
Get down and take cover!
[gunfire]
[AST GIRL 2-1] Are you sure
this is okay, Captain?
[RYOKO] We have permission
to smoke them out.
Once we've done our job,
the reinforcements can
take care of the rest.
[SHIDO]
Are you all right?
Hurry up and leave
while you still can.
I'd love to continue our talk,
but the last thing I want
is for you to get hurt.
Don't just stand there.
Get going before they open fire!
I'm staying right here!
Sit down. I wanna
talk some more!
You want to know about
this world, don't you?
So have a seat!
Pretend they're not even there!
[TOHKA] Alright.
[gunfire]
[SHIDO]
I'm curious.
If you're not human,
what exactly are you?
[TOHKA]
I don't know.
I don't remember
how long ago it was
when I appeared out of nowhere.
That's all I can recall.
Most of my oldest memories
are fuzzy and distorted.
I honestly don't know
what kind of being I am.
[SHIDO]
That's awful!
[TOHKA]
I suppose so.
My birth was sudden
and inexplicable,
and the Mecha-Mecha Squad was
already in the air when I awoke.
[SHIDO]
Mecha-Mecha huh?
[TOHKA] Them.
The noisy flying people.
[SHIDO] Interesting.
[KOTORI]
Here's your chance!
Her happiness meter
is over seventy.
Now's as good a time
as any to make a move.
[SHIDO]
What do you want me to do?
[KOTORI] For starters you
could ask her out on a date.
Uh...!
[TOHKA]
Hm? What's wrong?
Uh, nothing,
I'm just itchy.
You've been muttering under
your breath for a while.
Are you hiding
something from me?
[SHIDO] No, no,
you're overreacting!
Then tell me what you
were saying just now.
[SHIDO] I... forgot?
Come on. Cut to the
chase and ask her out.
Ask her out! Ask her out!
[GROUP] Ask her out!
All right already!
Shut up! I'll do it!
Tohka, I wanna
ask you something.
Um but it's-- Well,
it's kind of abrupt.
But, will you go out
on a date with me?
[gunfire]
Have we received any
new orders, Origami?
That's a negative, ma'am.
[RYOKO]
Even after all this?
Wait a minute.
Someone is down there
with the Spirit!
Hold on; hold your fire!
[gasps]
[RYOKO]
Origami, get back here!
What exactly is a date?
[SHIDO]
You don't know?
[KOTORI]
Look out! The AST!
Ahh!
[TOHKA]
How rude!
What? Tobiichi?
Stand back.
Well, if it isn't you again.
He's not your shield, you scum.
[SHIDO]
You've got it all wrong!
[RYOKO]
What are you doing, Origami?
We don't have orders
to break in on foot!
[TOHKA]
Sandalphon!
[KOTORI]
Shido, get out of there now!
The Fraxinus will
come to retrieve you.
And leave her here alone?
[ORIGAMI yells]
[helicopter sound]
[RYOKO] You could have
been killed out there!
Do you realize just how lucky
you are she became Lost?
Exercise some restraint. Okay?
You're a valuable
member of the AST.
So start acting like it!
[SHIDO] I was there
when everything happened.
Still, the massive destruction
just doesn't seem real.
But yesterday was real.
It wasn't a dream at all.
[TOHKA] Shido!
[SHIDO]
That's right.
I really did talk with
Tohka and give her a name.
--Crazy.
--Hey, Shido!
[TOHKA]
Quit ignoring me!
[SHIDO] Tohka!
You just now noticed me?
Wow, you are so dumb!
But how did you end
up back over here?
The spatial alarm
didn't even go off!
[TOHKA]
Why would it?
You were the one
who invited me back.
For a date I think?
Well guess what?
It's time for that date!
Let's go, let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, let's go!
Okay! Just bring
it down a bit!
And you should probably
get out of that first.
Do you mind changing?
Right now? You want me to
undress in broad daylight?
No, that's not it!
Lemme show
you an example.
You think this outfit is better?
Why are you walking
around with this picture?
[SHIDO] Quit asking questions,
just change already!
Very well.
How does this look?
[SHIDO]
Um, good.
Glad you think so.
Time for our date!
[SHIDO]
Hey, stop walking so fast!
[TOHKA]
You're too slow, Shido!
Date time, date time!
[SHIDO] Oh, sure, just
announce it to the entire world!