[SHIDO] The weather forecast
has been really off lately.
So much for only a ten
percent chance of rain.
Hey, are you okay?
Oh good.
You're not hurt?
Guess not, then.
[GIRL] Please.
Don't come any closer to me.
[SHIDO gasps]
[GIRL]
Don't hurt me.
Please, please don't hurt me.
[NARRATOR] The rain comes
from an unknown world,
washing the Earth
with its tears.
Is this new meeting
a temporary necessity,
or is it more likely to be
a contrived coincidence?
Because, as we all know,
there is more than one truth.
[TOHKA] Shido!
I made these things
called "cookies"!
We were supposed make
them during cooking class,
and the other students
taught me how!
So do you wanna try one?
[SHIDO]
Uh. Sure.
I'd love to; thanks!
Hey, Tobiichi.
Huh?
No way. You get out.
Be careful, Shido; that witch
is going to do more damage!
I'm so sorry.
[ORIGAMI] Although, I know
an apology is hardly enough.
[AI] Why is the Super
Genius apologizing to him?
What are we missing?
[MAI] Maybe he's
got some dirt on her.
[MII]
That's so lame.
Oh. It's fine.
You can stop bowing now.
Just don't worry about it. Kay?
Listen up. No more
cheating, okay?
Get your stinky hands off him!
The report said that you stayed.
Tell me what you're
still doing here.
[TOHKA] That's none
of your business!
Now focus, Shido.
Forget about the stupid, ugly
witch, and eat my cookies?
[ORIGAMI] And mine.
I baked cookies, too.
[TOHKA]
You need to stop copying me!
Actually, I baked mine first;
so you're copying me.
Wrong!
And besides, look at
your dumb cookies.
I bet they suck.
Oohhh...
Yeah. They're not all
that great, so here eat!
Quick, before she tries
to make you eat her junk.
No, you should try mine first.
[SHIDO]
Yum. They're both good.
Mine must be better;
he ate it much faster.
Incorrect. He ate mine point
two seconds faster than yours.
[TOHKA]
Excuse me?
Hey, some strange
little stranger
just gave me a whole
bag of cookies.
Do you want one, Shido?
I'd let her, but she's
watching her figure.
[SHIDO] Man, it wasn't
supposed to rain today, either!
Huh.
Hey, Kotori; I made it home.
I'm gonna go take a shower.
[gasps]
Get out of here right now!
[SHIDO]
Kotori, what's going on?
Why is Tohka here?
Hey! Welcome back home, bro!
[SHIDO]
Oh, thanks.
Don't change the subject!
Now, please tell me what
Tohka is doing in our house!
Well, I've decided she
should live with us--
you know, at least
for the time being.
Okay, do you mind
telling me why that is?
We have a good reason
for this. Chill.
[SHIDO] Reine?
What are you doing here?
Oh. Sorry.
Am I using too much sugar again?
[SHIDO] No. Well, yes but
I don't really care about that.
Tohka's aftercare?
That's right.
Fortunately,
when she kissed you,
her Spirit power was immediately
and effectively sealed.
And now, there is
an invisible road,
what we call a Path,
between the two of you.
[SHIDO] Okay, but what's
this thing about a seal?
I explained that to
you after it happened.
When you kissed Tohka after
raising her mood points,
you, in particular,
were able to absorb
her Spirit powers and seal them.
So why is it I have
that kind of power?
[KOTORI]
I'm not sure.
I just got lucky
and figured it out.
With Ratatoskr's help.
Can I continue with my point?
Now, if the Spirit's mental
condition becomes unstable,
there is a significant
probability that
the power sealed inside
you will return back to her.
Huh?
[REINE]
Our research is conclusive--
Tohka's numbers are the most
stable when she is near you.
Until the special housing unit
for Spirits is completed,
it would be best for
everyone if she stays here.
Right. Whatever.
This isn't a bad thing.
Consider it a part
of your training.
[SHIDO] You mean
I wasn't finished?
Tohka's powers are
already sealed,
what else am I supposed to do?
Did I say Tohka was
the only Spirit around?
There are more out there.
[REINE]
A lot more, in fact.
Special designation
disaster beings.
Also known as Spirits.
They come in all shapes
and sizes, just like us.
We want you to continue
speaking with them, Shin.
We need you to become even
better at dealing with women.
The world needs you to become
even better at
dealing with women.
Great. No pressure at all!
But I still don't get why
I have to live with Tohka!
I-I apologize, Shido.
I knew it. I shouldn't be here.
No. You're fine; I'm a jerk.
[SHIDO sighs]
This weird is never gonna end.
[KOTORI] Shido!
The light's out in the bathroom!
Go change it, immediately.
[SHIDO]
Of course.
Fine. I'm on it!
Why does she have to be so mean
when she's in her
"Commander" mode?
I'm normally the one to
do this stuff, but still.
[gasps]
Sorry; I'm so sorry!
I should have knocked.
[TOHKA]
Close the door, you creep!
[KOTORI]
Someone was in a rush.
Shame on Shido.
You did that
on purpose!
[KOTORI] I told you this
was training, didn't I?
You need to learn how
to face any situation
calm and collected.
[SHIDO]
Tohka. I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were in there.
It's fine; I forgive you.
Just hand that to me, please.
Shido, I got a bath
all ready for you.
You can go ahead and wash up.
Nah, I'm good. You go instead.
Oh, and here. You can
use these if you want.
Ah!
[SHIDO] Kotori has
never given up
first dibs when I've got these.
She should know not
to underestimate me.
I, Shido Itsuka, haven't grown
up in the same house as you
without learning a thing or two.
[KOTORI]
That's so nice.
But, uh-- why don't you
go ahead and use them.
Thanks, though.
[door opens]
[SHIDO]
Hey, Tohka.
You're not taking
a bath right now?
No, I'm standing in this door.
Maybe I was being
too suspicious.
Go figure there are
Spirits besides Tohka.
I wonder how many there are,
and will I be able
to save them all.
[TOHKA humming]
[SHIDO] Kotori,
I'm gonna kill you!
Not my fault you're dumb!
Oh crap!
Charge!
Hmm?
Ahh!
Um... Hi.
[SHIDO]
Calm down, Tohka!
[TOHKA] You can't just pop
out at me like that, you know!
[SHIDO]
I didn't pop. I said "hi"!
And another fail.
This is supposed
to be my training?
[TOHKA] Shido!
It's time for lunch.
Why are you here, witch?
You're not welcome.
I was going to say
the same thing.
Can't we all just eat together?
What? What is it?
Stare all you want;
I'm not sharing.
Excuse me.
What is that?
[SHIDO]
Oh. Um. The thing is--
this morning we bought our
bentos from the same place.
I bumped into Tohka
while she was there.
Liar.
You bought this one hundred
fifty-four days ago
at the discount store
in front of the station
for fifteen-eighty.
You've been using the
same container ever since.
This is not from
the bento shop.
And how, exactly,
do you know this?
That's not
really important.
Ugh. Don't leave me out of
the conversation like that;
it's rude.
Now, what are you
two talking about?
Hey! Shido.
My girlfriend wants me to
help her pick out clothes.
Do you think a
French Maid is best?
Shrine maiden,
nurse, maybe stripper?
Dude, this is
not the best time.
Who cares if she's a
maid or whatever else!
Maid it is! Thanks, man!
[alarm sounds]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Your attention, please.
This is not a drill. There
have been precursory signs
of an impending spatial
quake in this vicinity.
[SHIDO]
Not again.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
...nearest shelter immediately.
I repeat, there have
been precursory signs
of an impending spatial...
Kids! Another quake alarm!
We have to evacuate immediately!
Move it or lose it, as they say!
Leave?
[SHIDO] Yeah.
You want me to leave her behind?
Yes.
Remember, her powers
have been sealed,
so she's the same as
a normal human being.
Besides. We can't afford for
her stress levels to go up.
Watching a fight
might trigger that.
[SHIDO]
That's true.
[TAMAE]
Shido, Tohka, Miss Murasame,
why are you dawdling back there?
If you don't hurry
up and evacuate,
you're gonna be in serious
trouble and serious danger!
[SHIDO] Miss Okamine,
will you watch Tohka for me?
Huh? What?
Of course. I'll keep
an eye on her.
Shido.
Hey, Tohka. I need to
leave you here, okay?
Something just came up.
I have to go, but
I'll be right back.
Now? It's dangerous.
I'll be fine! I promise!
[TAMAE] Shido Itsuka,
come back here!
You too, Miss Murasame!
Where do you think you're going?
Oh, Shido.
Hey, you made it.
Well, for the aftermath, anyway.
It's smaller than
usual this time.
[KANNAZUKI] I'd like to
say this was a good sign,
but this is about
average for Hermit.
[SHIDO] Hermit?
[KOTORI] The name of the Spirit
that's appeared this time.
She's known for
being more docile
than the other
Spirits we've seen.
[gasps]
Hold on.
I've seen this girl before.
Where and when?
I met her at the shrine.
Two nights ago.
We were already
tracking her by then,
but we saw no disruption
of her main spirit wave
numbers at that time.
So, it's the same
as it was for Tohka.
[MINOWA]
The AST has arrived.
They're commencing their attack.
[gunfire]
How can they fire
on a little girl?
What she looks like
doesn't matter to the AST.
[SHIDO]
She's trying to run away!
What they're doing is wrong!
Don't feel sorry for her, Shido.
That behavior will
only make you weak.
Kotori!
Mmm?
[SHIDO] Let's do it.
I wanna go save that girl.
There ya go. That's so
my big brother for ya.
Listen up!
Prepare for a Type One Capture!
[GROUP] Right!
Okay. I think it's about
time we go on another date.
[RYOKO] Hermit has
entered the building.
AST, I want you to
hold your positions
until the target has moved.
[SHIDO] So, you think Hermit
is really going to come here?
[KOTORI] Yes. Based on the
analysis, there's no doubt.
The AST probably won't be able
to make a move for a while.
Don't tell me you're here
to bully Yoshinon, too.
[SHIDO] Ah!
Oh?
The lucky lecher has returned
for more, hasn't he?
[KOTORI]
Shido, hold on a sec!
[KOTORI] Talk to me people.
Name your choice.
[KAWAGOE] Come on.
It's gotta be Two.
This one's straight
out of a dating sim.
Go with Two!
[SHIIZAKI] Isn't that
risky if you don't know
the other person's personality?
Seems One is our best bet.
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Hermit rarely attacks humans.
I'm gonna have to go
with Option Three.
[KOTORI]
Shido, go with Three.
[SHIDO]
Uh. Are you sure about that?
[KOTORI]
Come on, don't you know someone
who would talk like that?
[SHIDO]
Tonomachi.
Excuse me?
I don't know what you mean;
I'm just a wandering vagabond.
[laughs]
You're trying to make
me laugh, aren't you?
Nobody talks like
that seriously.
Heh, heh. Well, I'm glad
you liked my joke.
So my name's Shido. You are?
Oh, I'm sorry;
how embarrassing.
I can't believe I forgot
to introduce myself to you.
My name is Yoshinon!
Idn'it cute? Idn'it cute?
Uh, yeah. Sure. It's cute.
So is that your name. Or is
it the name of the puppet?
Do you guys share a name?
[YOSHINON] Uh...
[KOTORI] Shido!
Her happiness meter just
went down dramatically!
What did you say to her?
What? Nothing; I swear.
I was just trying to find out
why she only talks
through ventriloquism.
[YOSHINON] I do not know what
you are talking about, Shido.
What is "ventriloquism"?
[KOTORI] Look, we'll figure
out the cause of this later.
For now just work on
making her happy again.
Right, yeah,
I get your point.
So, Yoshinon's
just Yoshinon?
[chuckles]
Oh, Shido, you're
one of those people
who jokes around a lot,
aren't you?
Why did you come here?
Oh, because--
Well, I know it's sudden.
But will-- will you
go on a date with me?
[YOSHINON] A date?
[TOHKA] Do you think it's really
all that dangerous outside?
[TAMAE] There's no telling
how dangerous it is,
but with a spatial quake,
it's not worth the risk.
Seriously?
Tohka doesn't know
about spatial quakes?
Maybe she's like a
spoiled, super rich girl.
That's so lame.
Miss Okamine,
why do you think
Shido would leave during
such a dangerous time?
Honestly.
I have no idea.
You don't?
She wants to save him.
She's totally brave.
I wanna be her
when I grow up.
That's so lame?
Well, I'm sure Shido
will be perfectly fine.
There's really nothing to
worry about, Tohka; you'll see.
Huh?
[ORIGAMI]
Permission to shoot?
[RYOKO] Not gonna
happen for a while.
We're talking about
weak little Hermit here.
She hasn't been that
much of a threat, yet.
Nothing worth city damage and
a call for support troops.
The conditions with
her are different
than those with Princess.
I still can't get over it.
A girl looking just like
Princess transfers into
your class without any
Spirit reactions detected.
There's seemingly nothing wrong
with her family
register, either.
I keep racking my brain
trying to figure it out,
but, to tell you the
truth, I got nothing.
[YOSHINON laughs]
[YOSHINON]
Tell me what you think!
Am I cool or am I
the coolest ever?
[SHIDO] Hey, wait;
that's not safe.
Hey, wait.
I asked if I was
cool or the coolest!
Ah, ah!
That-- that was, um--
I uh-- didn't mean.
[alarm sounds]
[SHIDO] Crap,
she's gonna be pissed.
Ow. Hahaha.
Sorry about that, Shido.
I wasn't paying
enough attention.
[KOTORI]
Shido, it's an emergency!
What? Emergency?
Tohka?
Shido, what were
you doing just then?
What do you mean?
So after you worried
me half to death,
you came here to
make out with her?
How dare you!
[KOTORI]
See what I mean.
You're looking at a rather
unstable mental condition.
Her Spirit powers are gradually
flowing back into her.
[SHIDO] Really?
What should I do?
How rude!
Why didn't you tell me this
"something that came up"
was meeting this weird
looking little girl!
[SHIDO]
No, um-- She's uh--
[YOSHINON]
Hello there, angry lady.
My name's Tohka!
[YOSHINON] I hate to be the
bearer of bad news, "Tohka,"
but it seems as though
Shido's gotten bored with you.
[gasps]
Based on what you've
already communicated,
Shido stood you up to come here
and hang out with me
instead, isn't that right?
I think that's
fairly conclusive.
No! What are
you talking a--
Shido, you shut your
mouth right now.
[SHIDO]
Okay.
[YOSHINON]
I do apologize, though.
Being second best is never
an easy thing, is it?
It's because I'm so charming,
not because there's anything
wrong with you, Tohka.
But, it's not like
you can blame Shido
for blowing you off so he
could come play with me.
I am pretty adorable.
No!
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
This can't be
happening! It can't!
[YOSHINON]
You can scream all you want.
But you're about to
hear the brutal truth.
Go on, Shido. Tell this poor
thing she's not wanted anymore.
I am too wanted!
You-- You don't know.
Shido is the one
who said it was okay
for me to stay here with him.
Why are you lying to
me and being so mean?
I won't take it anymore!
Say something!
C'mon, why aren't
you talking, now? Speak!
What's wrong? It won't talk.
Make it talk!
[HERMIT]
I was trying to talk.
Give it back, please.
[KOTORI] What are
you doing in there?
The Hermit's mental condition
is all over the place, too.
They need to calm down!
Hey. So, listen, Tohka?
Could you maybe give
that back to her, maybe?
Shido. She was right.
You really do like
her better than me.
[SHIDO]
No! It's not that at all.
Zadkiel!
[growls]
Uh. What's that?
[SHIDO yells]
[KOTORI] Oh no!
She's releasing her Angel!
This is bad.
You have to get
out of there now!
Her Angel?
[KOTORI] Did you forget
Tohka's Sandalphon?
[SHIDO]
Watch out!
[HERMIT yells]
[gunfire]
[ZADKIEL growls]
[ORIGAMI]
We lost her.
[RYOKO]
Everyone, return to base.
[SHIDO] You okay, Tohka?
You're not hurt?
I'm alright.
Will you just get away?
[SHIDO]
But, why?
Don't touch me!
[SHIDO winces]
Ah!
You like that little girl
better than me, I know you do.
Admit it!
Wait. What?
That's perfect.
Looks like someone's
got trouble in paradise.