No way. It can't be.
If you think
your flames
are gonna scare me,
you're wrong!
Cause you're not the
only one with a cool toy!
[NARRATOR] Spirits
are not human beings.
And human beings are
certainly not Spirits.
Even though they
have some similarities,
their differences
abound. Poor Shido.
He's far more than
slightly confused.
[KURUMI laughs]
Now then.
How about you and I engage
in a little bit of
Spirited competition?
Is this really
the best you can do?
I have to say, I'm unimpressed!
You can call forth an Angel,
and command flames,
surely you can beat
little ole me, can't you?
Oh well, I guess not!
Why don't you
keep your mouth shut?
You're a lot cuter
when you're not talking!
Well, I happen to think
you would be a lot cuter
with your pretty little
head mounted on my wall!
Zaphkiel! Zayin!
Guys, stop it! Please!
It must really suck
to be you right now.
Frozen in time and
completely surrounded.
Oh well.
Bye-bye, flame girl.
[KURUMI] A pointblank
shot to the noggin'.
That'll sure dampen
your Spirit, eh?
It really is too bad,
I was actually
starting to enjoy her.
And now she's dead.
[KURUMI] Now
that that's settled,
you're on deck, Shido.
Let's have a little fun--
[KOTORI] Monologue-ing
always gets
the bad guy in trouble.
Not part of your plan?
If you'd rather tuck your
tail between your legs
and run home to mommy,
I'd completely understand.
Ha! Not in your wildest
dreams, flame girl!
Aleph!
What are you doing?
[KOTORI] Cut her
to pieces! Camael!
[KURUMI] Damn you!
Come, Zaphkiel! Daletto!
[KOTORI] Ah, come on,
don't give up on me already.
You can't quit just
when your opponent
is warmed up, it's bad form!
[KURUMI] I promise you this:
You'll be sorry you ever
decided to mess with me!
Zaphkiel!
Hmph. Yeah!
Show me what you got!
[KOTORI] What's happening?
Kotori!
[KURUMI] It looks like
your devil's luck has run out!
[SHIDO] Kotori!
Are you all right?
Camael. Megiddo!
Rally to me immediately!
Turn them all to ashes!
Do it, Camael!
[KOTORI] Pick up your weapon.
This fight's
not over yet.
And the war's not
over yet, either!
Well? Come on then.
Let's have some more
of that destruction
you love so much!
This is the fight you wanted!
This is the war
you wanted, isn't it?
[KOTORI] If you can't
face the muzzle
of a gun anymore it's over.
Time for you to die.
Kotori!
If you keep pushing
like this, she will die!
[SHIDO] Isn't the
point of Ratatoskr
to resolve conflicts
without killing Spirits?
You have to stop!
[SHIDO] Stay back!
No. Don't. Please.
Big Brother, look out!
[quiet sobbing sounds]
Huh?
Big Brother! Big Brother!
[YOSHINON] Would you
like me to operate?
[YOSHINO] Yes, please.
Thank you, Doctor.
All righty then.
Nurse, please
hand me my scalpel!
Oh. I was playing
doctor. Sorry.
You're fine.
[SHIDO] Tohka. She's here, too?
Why am I in a sick bay?
[REINE] Well.
You're awake. That's good.
Looks like the
anesthesia didn't work.
Good thing you woke up
before I cut you open.
I really am sorry.
I hope I didn't scare you.
Please. I'm fine, really.
Hey, Reine. Tell me.
What am I doing in here?
The thing is you
were knocked out
in the battle with Kurumi,
so we brought you here
just to be on the safe side.
Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
But I don't know what
happened after that!
What about Tohka?
She's just sleeping, isn't she?
Hey. Where is Kotori?
What was that power?
You need to
calm down, Shin.
No, I'm not
gonna calm down!
Wait, what about Kurumi?
And Mana, is she all right?
And everyone from school?
Everything'll
be just fine.
Do you feel better now?
Yeah.
Everybody is doing okay,
and no one was killed.
All things considered,
it could've been much worse.
[REINE] As far as
Origami. And Mana.
They were both taken
by members of the AST.
We can't be certain yet,
but our best guess is they were
brought to Tengu Hospital.
Kurumi ran off
while she had the chance.
And as you can see,
Tohka is sleeping.
Even though she's hurt,
she wanted to be by your side.
Tohka cares more about you
than she does her own recovery.
Not to worry though,
she's gonna be fine.
That's good, but
this isn't the end, is it?
Of course not.
Kotori. Can I see her?
[REINE] She can't hear or see
us through the protective wall.
[REINE] You're going to
be on your own in there.
[KOTORI] Hey you.
I didn't expect to
see you up and about.
How are you feeling?
Better. I guess.
What about you?
Are you feeling okay?
I feel like my normal
super cute self.
Not sure it's normal
to call yourself cute.
You don't
think I'm cute?
No. You're right,
I guess you're kinda cute.
But Kotori, tell me the truth,
are you really a Spirit?
[SHIDO] Answer me.
Are you a Spirit or not?
[KOTORI] Well, if I told
you that I wasn't a Spirit,
would you believe me?
Of course. If you
said so, then I would.
Is that right?
You'd believe what someone says
even when you've seen
the contrary to be true.
If you want my two cents,
that seems like a fast way
to make a fool of yourself.
If I can't even
trust my little sis,
what kinda brother
would that make me?
Look, I said I'd believe you.
I always will, no matter what.
I think
I'm a human being.
I mean I wouldn't
call myself a Spirit.
Although, the
observation equipment
might beg to differ.
I have no doubt the machine
says I'm lying to you.
[SHIDO] Wait, what do you mean?
I was born into
the Itsuka family,
and that much I know for sure.
But five years ago.
Somehow, I became
a Flame Spirit.
[KOTORI] That may not
be the best way to put it.
I guess it's more
accurate to say I became
a person who
possesses Spirit powers.
[SHIDO] Seriously?
[SHIDO] This might sound nuts,
but I knew about this.
That's impossible!
I never said anything to you!
No. No, that's
not what I'm saying.
I had this dream.
[YOUNG SHIDO] Kotori! No!
[YOUNG KOTORI] Big brother!
Big Brother, no!
[quiet sobbing]
[YOUNG KOTORI] Big Brother.
I'm sorry Brother!
[KOTORI] I have to say,
I'm not sure I agree
with the part where
I was screaming out
for you and crying
like a big baby.
But more or less,
that's the way
I remember it, too.
It's possible it may
have flowed to yo
through the path
when the Spirit powers
returned to me.
I see. But I still
don't get it.
What happened? How did
you become a Spirit?
I wish I could tell you;
but the truth is,
I don't remember.
[SHIDO] Huh?
[KOTORI] I mean,
obviously I know something
must've happened back then.
But for the life of me,
I don't know what.
I remember becoming a Spirit
but I don't know how.
Or even why for that matter.
[SHIDO] How can you forget
something so important?
Look who's talking.
You're in no position
to pass judgment
on the forgetful front, Big Bro.
[KOTORI] But then again,
you're right.
It's kinda weird
that neither one of us
has any memory of it at all.
You'd think we would
remember everything.
Who knows?
Maybe somebody
erased our memories
for some reason.
Well, it's a theory anyway.
After that, I was
discovered by Ratatoskr.
Then I found out
the truth about
what was going on
behind the scenes.
And I decided I wanted
to save the Spirits.
[SHIDO] But once you
got past that big fire,
you lived a pretty typical life.
How were you able to blend
in with the regular kids?
[KOTORI] What, you don't
remember that part either?
I was able to be a normal girl
because you sealed
away my Spirit powers.
[SHIDO] Really?
Wait, are you serious?
Yeah. Didn't
I tell you yesterday?
[KOTORI] Don't let me forget
to give this back to you, Shido.
I don't fully
understand why.
But for some
inexplicable reason,
you're able to seal
away a Spirit's power,
and that's why you were chosen
by Ratatoskr to
talk to the Spirits.
You're special, Shido.
[SHIDO] So my regeneration
ability came from--?
Ugh, yes, your ability
came from mine.
Now. Listen up.
Come over here and stand
right in front of me.
[SHIDO] Why should I do that?
Cause I said so.
[SHIDO] Fine.
I told ya to be
careful, didn't I?
But you didn't listen to me.
If I hadn't
come to my senses,
you'd be dead meat.
You're very lucky.
What the heck were you
thinking anyway, you idiot,
running out in front of
my line of fire like that?
[SHIDO] You scared me.
I thought you'd lost it.
And I was right.
You weren't yourself.
Yeah.
When the Spirit
powers returned to me,
I lost control.
All I wanted to do
was break something.
Or better yet, kill someone
if I got the chance.
I was scared.
It was like I was
a different person.
Who knows what
other awful things
I've done that
I have no memory of.
There's no telling.
If it's that easy for me to
lose control over myself,
I wouldn't be shocked
if I already have
killed someone!
[SHIDO] Stop
talking like that!
Just ignore me.
I don't even know
what I'm talking about.
But I do think I know why
I snapped out
of it yesterday.
It's because you
stepped in front of me.
Thanks for saving
the day, big bro.
About your Spirit power,
will it come back to me?
I don't really know.
Unfortunately, Spirit stuff
isn't always easy to understand.
All I know for sure is this:
you'll have to seal it
just like you did before.
But to seal it away,
I'd have to--
[KOTORI] Yes, take me on a
date and make me fall in love.
The same way you did with Tohka.
And Yoshino. You have to.
[SHIDO] Hey. Kotori!
Are you all right?
Can you stand?
Yeah, I'm okay.
You don't need
to worry about me.
Please. Talk to me.
Shin. That's enough
for today, all right?
You go ahead, I'll
handle things from here.
No, I can't.
[REINE] We'll have
lots to discuss later.
But for now, go on.
Okay.
[TOHKA] Shido! I've
been looking everywhere!
I was worried 'cause when
I woke up you were gone.
But you're awake.
So does this mean
you're feeling better?
I don't know.
Do you mind
if we talk later?
Eh.. Yeah, okay.
[REINE] I give her two days.
I doubt she'll last
much longer than that.
Eventually, her
Spirit power will be
too much for her to handle.
[SHIDO] Whaddya mean by that?
[REINE] Once the power
overtakes her completely,
Kotori will no longer
be anything like
the little sister you
once knew and loved.
In just under forty-eight hours,
we'll have you go
on a date with her.
That'll be your best
chance to make sure
she doesn't slip away forever.
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST A]
Sorry sir,
but you're not
allowed to see her.
Not even her family
can do that yet.
I do apologize,
but I'm afraid I don't know
when she's going to
be allowed visitors.
[SHIDO] But why?
Is it really that bad?
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST A]
I wish I could help.
But unfortunately, at this time,
I can't discuss her
condition with you.
Ma'am, please.
[ORIGAMI] Shido.
[SHIDO] Origami.
[ORIGAMI] I'm glad
you're safe. Is Tohka okay?
Uh. Yeah.
She's uh-- She's good.
[ORIGAMI] Never mind.
So. You came here
to see Mana, huh?
Yeah, well.
I tried to but the
nurse wouldn't allow it.
I can't go into
specifics but--
For Mana's recovery,
they're using some highly
classified equipment on her.
So until she's moved
to the general ward,
there's no way they'll
let anyone see her.
[ORIGAMI] And if you
try to force your way in.
It won't end well.
[ORIGAMI] I know
that's why you're here.
[SHIDO] Huh?
To see Mana and nobody else.
Oh. Well obviously,
I came to visit you, too!
[ORIGAMI] Uh huh.
[SHIDO] Yeah,
I'd better get a move on.
I'm sure you're really busy.
I bet you have lots
of doctors' appointments
and stuff like that. Later!
[thud]
[SHIDO] Origami!
Are you all right?
I can't make it back
to my room on my own.
Will you please carry me?
[SHIDO] I should get a nurse.
Carry me, right now.
[SHIDO] Come on,
who needs a nurse?
Can you walk?
No, I can't.
[SHIDO] What you
need is a wheel chair.
I'll get one.
No, please stop,
I can't handle that.
I'll vomit from
motion sickness.
What do you expect
me to do about it?
Piggyback me.
Huh?
[ORIGAMI] You heard me.
Right.
[SHIDO] Hey, Origami.
Don't you think you're
holding on a little tight there?
[ORIGAMI] Um, no.
You're in room
'three-oh-five' all the way
in the west wing, aren't you?
[SHIDO] Okay, that tickles!
Please! Don't!
[ORIGAMI] Man up.
[SHIDO] Uh, Origami, stop.
[ORIGAMI pants]
[SHIDO grunts] Oh boy.
All right, that's enough!
Hey! Licking is
crossing the line, okay?
[SHIDO] Well then.
I'm just gonna go ahead and go.
Peel it.
Uh. Well, I suppose
I could make that happen.
Now feed it to me.
Don't you think this
is getting a little crazy?
You wanna see crazy,
try not feeding me.
Now put it in my mouth.
Fine, here!
[moans and slurps]
Um. Please stop.
Wait, don't stop. No, do.
It's gross. And awesome, too.
Oh god. Too much!
Delicious.
Great. I'm glad to
hear you liked it.
So anyway,
I'm gonna take off now.
[ORIGAMI] But what
about my temperature?
I'm gonna need your help.
Sticking it in my mouth.
Oh, all right! Fine!
[SHIDO] Why am I sitting down
to take your temperature?
This is inappropriate!
What the heck is going on?
Well, you seemed
to get excited by
Kurumi's behavior.
Since you like
that sort of thing,
I thought I'd turn up the
volume and get more aggressive.
Here are the
rules, big boy.
If you look, you have to touch.
[SHIDO] Goodbye, Origami.
I'm really leaving this time.
[ORIGAMI] Can I ask
you one more thing?
[ORIGAMI] It's important.
I want you to tell
me what happened
after the fight with
Kurumi Tokisaki yesterday.
Because I thought
I saw another Spirit,
floating in the sky.
She was surrounded
by flames.
Flames she could control.
[ORIGAMI] Then
I must've passed out.
The next thing I knew,
I woke up in here,
so I want you to
tell me what I missed.
No matter how
insignificant the details.
I want to know
everything that happened,
and everything you know
about this Flame Spirit.
Oh. Well uh...
I got knocked out, too,
so I don't know much.
Why do you ask?
[ORIGAMI] Just curious.
[SHIDO] Well, do you know her?
The Flame Spirit, I mean?
[ORIGAMI] Yes, I do.
Five years ago there was a
massive fire in Tengu City.
It mainly broke out in
a small neighborhood
called Nankou, and
that's when I first saw her.
The day she burned
my parents alive.
[YOUNG KOTORI] Big Brother!
[ORIGAMI] Ever since
she killed my family,
I've spent every waking
moment searching for her.
[ORIGAMI] No one
should ever have
to feel the way I felt that day.
She's the reason
I joined the AST.
The reason I trained
as hard as I could.
She's why I get out
of bed in the morning
and she's what I think
about when I go to sleep.
I promised myself back then that
when I had the chance,
I wouldn't hesitate.
I'd wrap my hands
around her throat,
look her in the eyes,
and crush every last
bit of remaining life.
And now my opportunity
is right in front of me.
This is the moment
I've been waiting for.
[ORIGAMI] I swear to you.
I will kill the Flame Spirit.