-What?
-I'm gonna teach her a lesson.
I won't take anymore threats.
I'm gonna prove to her
that we're stronger together.
To do that...
I need to have
lots of negative points.
No stop!
I'll give my entire
left hand to the King.
Natsuko! What are you
gonna do now?
No!
[NOBUAKI]
Stop it. Please, you can't!
Teruaki!
One more left.
Probably don't need
a thumb, anyway.
All right, Natsuko.
Give me and Nobuaki
our phones back.
Or these are all yours.
Five negative points
you'll have to make up somehow
if you don't want to die.
You talk a big game,
but can you do this?
Your entire right hand.
You'll have to mangle every one
of your fingers to zero out.
So, what's it gonna be?
[NATSUKO] If I do give you
your phones back,
then who are those
negative points going to?
[TERUAKI] My left hand
will never heal completely.
I'm done.
My dream is over.
There's no point in me
living anymore.
I don't know what
I'd do with myself now.
Don't say that.
Hurry it up!
Do you have the guts
to break your fingers
to save yourself from dying?
Fine, take the phones.
Who cares?
Will you get 'em?
I give one positive point
to Nobuaki,
four negatives to Natsuko,
and one negative to Aimi.
The hell?
You're up next, Natsuko.
You have to break
four fingers to live.
If I were you, I'd get crackin'.
That wasn't the deal!
You said you'd give
the points to yourself
if I gave you back
your stupid phones!
No, you're very mistaken
about that.
All I said for sure was that
I wouldn't give you five.
Or, you could always pass,
of course.
There are still
four people after you
who have to take turns.
Just four positive points
from them and you'll survive.
Pretty risky move.
You'd have to trust
that each one of them
would be willing to sacrifice
a finger for you,
like I did for Nobuaki.
Do you think they care
about you that much?
Teruaki.
This rock did the trick for me.
Consider it a present.
[laughs]
[NATSUKO breathing shakily]
I don't need that thing.
-I pass.
-What'd you say?
A little louder, please!
Pass!
[TERUAKI chuckles] You're
too afraid to hurt yourself.
Even though you've
played with our lives
as if we didn't mean anything.
Do you honestly think any of us
are gonna step up
to protect you now?
Oh, yeah.
Have you figured out
why I gave one of the negative
points to Aimi and not you?
It's 'cause
she asked me to do it.
In fact, we had this whole thing
planned before you got here.
What is he talking about, Aimi?
Why are you scheming against me?
[RYOU]
That looks really bad.
Do you think you should go
to the hospital?
No. I wanna see
everything go down.
Are you sure?
I mean, I get it.
But you don't wanna
lose that hand.
Don't worry about it.
It's just some broken bones.
Besides, it's not like
I gave my left hand to Natsuko
and Aimi just to get
our phones back.
Sure, but
giving up your dream
to get some revenge
is a hell of a trade.
No, it's not like that.
Seriously.
This wasn't about revenge.
We remember what you said
about the Game.
All of us have to come together
as a group to survive.
And to do that,
we need a real leader
who can guide us
through this nightmare.
That's why he made this plan.
So the rest of us'll live.
-[MATSUOKA] I pass.
-[NOBUAKI/RYOU] Uh...
[RIONA]
I pass as well.
[RINA]
Yeah, so do I.
[NOBUAKI]
None of them gave fingers.
-So...
-It's my turn.
[NATSUKO]
Please, you've gotta save me!
Unless you break the fingers
on your right hand, I'll die!
It's the only way!
Help me, Aimi!
Is that it?
Don't you have anything else
to say to me?
I don't want
to get killed this way!
Please, Aimi, I'm begging you.
Snap your fingers for me!
That's really all?
Well, I tried.
You know what?
This'll come in handy after all.
[NOBUAKI]
Aimi! Run!
[giggles]
[AIMI]
Tell me, Natsuko.
What do you see
when you look at me right now?
What do I mean to you?
What Teruaki said was true.
I asked him to give me
one negative point.
I wanted to know
if you would save me.
If you'd protect me
when my life was in danger.
I was ready to sacrifice my hand
for you no matter what.
All you had to do
was give me one positive point.
Simple as that. But no.
In the end, you only care
about yourself
and winning this, don't you?
I only wanted
to hear you say one thing.
That we were friends.
That's all.
Tell me, Natsuko.
Are we friends?
[screaming]
[AIMI crying]
You would go this far?
She's supposed to be
your best friend!
You won't stop me.
There's no way I can lose now!
You can't really be that stupid.
Why would anyone
in their right mind
give you their positive points
after you did that to them?
Moron.
Shows how much you know about
how people react to extremes.
Times like this, you can push
someone to do anything.
Aimi! Think of everything
we've been through!
Hurry and give me those points!
No. Why?
Why are we hurting each other?
I thought we were supposed
to look out
for one another, Natsuko,
but you've hurt me so much.
Watch, when people
are staring into the void.
When they're at the edge,
they don't make
rational decisions, Nobu.
You've seen it, too,
haven't you?
All the horrors
that I went through.
They taught me how easily
we can betray one another.
People say that they'll
help you, but it's just talk.
-Pretty lies.
-Shut your mouth!
But I'm different!
I can save you.
Isn't that right, Aimi?
The same way I did back then!
-Natsuko?
-Hey, Aimi.
Do you want to join
the track team?
It's a great way
to get to know new people.
Well, I'm not that
interested in sports,
plus I have asthma,
so I don't really run much.
That's why you should!
I actually did some research.
I learned that working
on breath control
and getting more
physically fit can totally help
with someone's asthma problems!
Yeah, but I have no stamina.
No worries!
Everybody starts out that way.
Plus, I'll be there to cheer you
on the whole time!
I'll stay by your side.
Because we're friends!
No. Aimi, why?
I have to.
If I don't, Natsuko will die!
You can't be serious
right now, Aimi.
You still want
to protect her
even though
she ruined your hand?
She was just scared, that's all.
She was driven to the brink.
What else could she have done?
This is what it means
to care for someone.
This time, I'll be the one
to save Natsuko's life.
I just don't understand it.
Think, Aimi.
Can you honestly tell me
this is what friendship's about?
To me, friendship's about...
our past.
[ALL gasp]
Look. You and I are always
gonna be friends, Natsuko.
And I'll trust you
no matter what happens.
I hereby give my four
positive points over to you.
Aimi, I'm sorry you had
to do that for me.
Thank you so much.
-[bones crack]
-[screaming]
Your thumb's the thickest one.
I bet that means it's pretty
hard to break on your own hand.
So I did it for you, my friend.
You're really gonna say
you did that for her
and not because you're
some kinda sick sadist?
Of course.
After all, it was
the only way left
that I could save her life.
If I know her, I'm guessing
she was just going
to let herself die.
I couldn't allow that to happen.
[AIMI crying]
Now calm down, Aimi.
Give yourself the last point,
and you'll be back
at zero, perfectly safe.
Then this game will be over.
Natsuko?
Okay. I'll give one
positive point to myself.
It's over now.
We survived.
We're fine!
[crying]
[NOBUAKI]
This is wrong.
Natsuko, do you really think
this is what friendship is,
or is it all a ploy?
Either way, you're crazy.
-[AIMI continues crying]
-[phone beeping
[ALL murmuring]
Aimi, how bad is your hand?
Is it gonna be okay?
Natsuko, I have to ask.
Are you gonna change the way
you play the game
after what happened today?
Seeing what Aimi did for you
must have made you look
at your actions
differently, somehow.
What exactly
am I supposed to change?
And if I did play differently,
do you think
the King's Game
would suddenly just end?
We both know
what's gonna happen, Nobuaki.
Maybe my King's Game was
a little different than yours,
but, still.
The choices I had to make
in the end were clear.
Hold on. What was different
when you played?
Oh, I'll tell you that later.
First I have to make sure
to show the rest of our class
that this hope you have
of saving everyone is idiotic.
It's just gonna get them killed.
Get our class together.
We'll meet under
the Yatsuhashi Bridge real soon.
[NOBUAKI] You're still
the same twisted girl.
[grunts]
-What's that for?
-Sorry.
Just tryin' to lighten
the mood a little bit, you know.
And kicking me helps?
Whoa. Oh, man.
That's not lookin' so good.
Yeah. The doctor said
I'll never use it again.
Come on. Don't look so sad.
I don't regret a thing
I did back there.
Besides, my right hand is good.
I've still got
a lot to live for.
That's true.
We have to follow our dreams.
And I'm not giving up.
I'll become a stylist someday,
just with one hand.
Man, I'm gonna have to cut
your hair again soon, huh?
Sure.
Hey, wait.
Where's Ryou?
I figured he'd still be
out here.
Oh, actually,
he took off saying he wanted
to get you a present.
Just a little something
to celebrate you leaving
the hospital.
Wow. It's not like I even
had an overnight stay.
-But I appreciate it.
-It's nice.
And he'll be glad
to hear you're okay.
I've never seen such
a supportive friend.
[chuckles]
-[TERUAKI] Shall we?
-Yeah.
[MASATOSHI] Hey, man.
What'd they say about your hand?
It'll be just fine.
The doc said I should be good
as new in about two months.
[sighs]
We've got bigger things
to worry about right now,
like what we're gonna do next.
Even though I've played
the King's Game before,
I have no idea what
the next order's gonna be.
All I'm sure of
is that it's my goal
to keep any of us
from getting punished.
And since I don't know
how to end this game early,
right now we just gotta stick
together as long as we can.
Look, I won't ask you
to trust me.
But will you at least trust
each other going forward?
All you gotta do
is share your will to live.
Make sure you're always
helping each other out.
-Please, guys.
-He's right.
I am not giving up
on my life yet.
We can survive this together.
I trust him. And all of you.
Well, if you insist.
I've got too much to live for.
Yeah, I'm not gonna let
some stupid text game
be the end of me.
-Me, neither.
-We can beat this.
-Thank you.
-Well, I think that settles it.
But we need you
to lead us Nobuaki.
Show us the best way
to get through this damn game.
-I'll try my--
-[NATSUKO] That's pointless.
[NOBUAKI]
Natsuko.
A leader just takes away
your free will.
The only one who can save you
from death is yourself.
-You really believe that?
-You're damn right.
We only have about ten minutes
before the next order
is due to come in
from the King.
So I suggest that you get ready
to play instead of whining.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry, are you gonna
run away with your tail
between your legs instead?
What kind of man are you--
It's obvious today didn't
affect you in the slightest.
Think of what happened.
Teruaki. And Aimi, your friend.
They offered their lives
to prove a point.
I thought it would've opened
your eyes a little bit at least.
Opened my eyes?
You're the one who's walking
around blind in this game.
Do you know what I meant
when I said your insane hope
will end up
getting them all killed?
What is wrong with you?
You're just a liar.
You know only one person
can survive the game.
And even if you do survive,
it keeps going.
So don't try to pretend
this will end happily.
We may as well start killing
to stay alive.
You're wrong. One day, all of
our efforts and research will--
Will you stop being so naive?
Hey, I've got
a question for you.
-What is it?
-If that's really how you feel,
then why'd you force Aimi
to live in the last game?
By your own logic, shouldn't
you have left her thumb alone
and simply watched her die?
I owed her a favor.
That's all that was.
I'm gonna let you in
on something.
Unlike him,
at the end of my game,
I had to kill the person
I hated the most.
Even now, just thinking about
them makes me want to vomit.
They toyed
with people's hearts,
ruined the lives
of everyone they crossed,
and died so easily.
There was one person
I really wanted to protect,
but they threw themselves
off of a cliff.
Without saying goodbye.
That was the hardest part.
All of a sudden,
they were just gone.
-Disappeared forever.
-Natsuko.
[phones beeping, chiming]
I win, Nobuaki.
One more down.
Uh...
But the text says
he broke the rules.
Are you telling me that you
somehow forced him to do it?
Kind of. I guess
you could say that.
No way.
[screams]
-[NOBUAKI] Teruaki!
-[gasping]
I'm sorry. Really.
-I didn't see this coming.
-No. Why?
Why am I the one
who's being punished?
I did nothing wrong.
What rule did I break?
You're so dumb.
I shouldn't be surprised
that you didn't lock your phone
with some kind of security code.
While I had it, I just blocked
the King's number,
which, as you know,
is basically a death sentence.
The rules clearly say
you can't leave the game
partway through the fun.
We all know what
the goddamn rules are!
He did ask
why this happened.
And since I answered
his question,
he should be thanking me
right now.
-You murderer!
-[coughs, spits]
Hang in there.
There's one good thing. Ryou.
At least he's not here
to see me dying.
He's too sensitive.
He couldn't handle
something like this.
So much blood.
It'd ruin him.
Come on, man,
save your strength.
[groans, gasps]
Sorry I couldn't do much
to help in the end.
I guess this is it for me.
Goodbye.
You're wrong about that.
You gave me so much hope.
You filled all of us
with courage.
You brought us together.
You have no idea how much
you did for us, Teruaki.
Promise.
You won't give up. Ever.
Survive. Finish this.
Take care of them.
Lead them.
One day...
I'm gonna cut...
[gasps]
...your hair again.
[body thuds]
[screaming, crying]
[BOY]
No!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
So, if you don't really
want to play,
then you should block
the King now.
It's the easiest way
to escape this hellish game.
-Simple as that.
-You did this! Not him!
-You're a freakin' psychopath!
-Oh, am I?
Well, at least I'm still alive.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You killed him.
No one has the right to steal
someone else's life like that.
Teruaki didn't want to die.
He still had dreams
and a future
he was looking forward to.
Please, we both know
that's not true.
His hand was never gonna heal.
He just didn't want to accept
that he was finished.
In fact, he was probably
contemplating suicide.
His head's right there, Nobuaki.
Why don't you ask him for us?
You're a monster!
I think dying might be
easier than playing anymore.
You're right.
No. Hurry, Natsuko,
go stop her.
Stop her? I guess.
Just don't get the wrong idea.
I'm doing this for me.
Sorry, Aimi. My dear.
But I need you
to keep on living.
You're gonna have
to save me again later.
[NOBUAKI]
Is this right? Or wrong?
I can't tell
the difference anymore.
-[package drops on ground]
-Uh...
Ryou!
Hey, Nobuaki. What's going on?
What's that?
Why's Teru on the ground?
Look, I bought you a hat!
It took a while, but I finally
found one that's perfect.
[sobbing]
Isn't it cool? I hope it fits.
[chuckles]
Ryou, Teruaki's gone.
What's wrong?
Don't you like it?
Hey, Nobuaki.
Why isn't Teru smiling, huh?
I spent so much time
picking out a hat,
but he doesn't look
happy about it.
There.
Come on,
why aren't you smiling?
Your best friend got you
a great present!
Stop it.
Please just put him down.
[RYOU]
Smile, Teru.
Let's see those pearly whites!
[NOBUAKI] Little by little,
everyone's starting to break.
What's wrong. Come on!
Smile! Please?
[RYOU laughing]
[NOBUAKI]
They're losing their humanity.
Soon there'll be nothing left.