Where are you, Nobuaki?
I'm supposed to meet you.
Akamatsu. Kenta.
It's Kenta?
Wow, is the whole class here?
Are you guys out here
to celebrate the big sports
day win or something?
Huh? Ah!
What the? Is that...
a body?
Nobuaki!
Hey. You look pretty bad.
Who did this to you?
What the hell? Do something!
[KENTA] He's really hurt.
You have to help him!
Wait a sec. You did it.
No. I mean, yeah,
but we had to.
-He brought it on himself.
-What?
You had to gang up on him
and beat him half to death?
I don't care whatever you think
Nobuaki deserves.
I'm not gonna let you lynch him.
Instead, you can fight me.
[thunder rumbles]
Kenta.
Nobuaki?
Try to stay awake, bro.
[coughs]
Hey. Thank you, man.
Don't thank me.
Tell me what happened.
What the hell's going on?
And what's with
that bloody mess?
-It's Yuuichi.
-What? No way.
Uh, what are you doing? C'mon.
Put on some clothes!
Oh, shut up.
You're interrupting.
We were just getting
to the fun part.
You think this is fun?
One of your classmates
has been killed!
You're really starting
to annoy me.
Send this.
But...
No! Why Kenta, too?
Mizuki, if you don't send
this text to two people,
you're going to be murdered.
You don't want to die.
Well, no.
Then show us
what beautiful deaths
the King has planned
for those two.
Pretty please?
[MIZUKI] I don't get it.
Why are you acting so strange?
I'm not. I'm trying to help.
I'm just looking out
for you, Mizuki.
No! I can't do this.
It's way too messed up!
Mizuki...
you gotta do it. Text me.
Send the other one to Natsuko.
There's no way I can do that!
I can't kill someone!
It's wrong.
I don't want to do it.
I'm not a murderer!
Oh, no.
What have I done?
-You dumb cow.
-But wait...
[MIZUKI] I can just buy
a new phone, can't I?
-It'll be okay. Right?
-It's too late.
[Mizuki cries]
[NATSUKO]
Ugh, what a buzzkill.
Teruaki, let's get out of here.
-[Mizuki cries]
-Uh, hold on.
Oh, I didn't know you wanted
to die like Yuuichi.
You're not going anywhere!
Our classmate is
on the ground over there.
You can't leave.
We gotta stop this.
I agree.
What? He has a good point.
Crap.
I'm taking him
to the emergency room!
Hold on, okay?
Yeah? What is it?
I'm going to
the hospital with you.
I don't want to be here.
Yeah, that's cool.
We can go together.
In that case,
won't you let me tag along, huh?
I cannot deal with this chick.
We're going.
Um, Natsuko?
I'm scared.
What should I do now.
I don't want to die,
but there's no way out of it.
[KENTA] Don't worry.
I'll fix this, you'll see.
Fix this?
And how is that going to work?
Don't say you're gonna
make things better
when there's nothing
you can do.
You're gonna be fine.
I keep my promises.
Look at this.
It's the order I got earlier.
[MIZUKI] He made you the King?
What are you gonna do?
I'll send it to myself,
saying "Protect
Yukimura Mizuki.
Save her. Make sure
that she survives this."
How does that sound?
If I don't follow the order,
I'll die, too.
So you know I'll do
everything to protect you.
Kenta, thanks.
This King's Game thing
is such a mess.
The others were talking
as if it's all Nobuaki's fault
or something.
So, is it? What's the deal?
Yeah. It's true.
It's my fault.
I got you all involved.
Yuuichi, too.
I may as well have
murdered him myself.
This isn't the first time.
I did things I can't take back
in the last game, too.
Be honest with us.
What happened to you back then?
[MAMI]
Nobuaki, is it true?
[MINAKO]
No. Daisuke can't be dead!
If he is,
then Hideki and Satomi
weren't just
a weird coincidence.
It's the game. That's the only
thing I'm sure of.
The King's Game
is totally real.
Impossible. Like,
I didn't think he would die.
Listen up. All of us got
the new order, right?
Wait, you can't be serious.
[NOBUAKI] I think we have to
do the poll.
Are you a lunatic?
If we do that,
the loser might be murdered!
She's right. You're basically
asking us to kill a classmate.
Don't even joke about that.
We have to do it.
If we don't vote, both of us
will be punished.
That means we have no choice.
-Then, it's settled.
-Uh, yeah.
Let's agree here and now
that we won't blame anyone.
No matter what happens,
we chose to do this.
[NOBUAKI] We'll cast our votes
at noon today.
In order to win this,
you need at least 16 votes.
Chiemi and I
will talk to the girls.
I bet we can sway
a few of them.
I don't think there's any way
we can convince them all,
but I'm close
to Kaori and Emi.
I can get them on our side.
Naoya, you talk
to the guys, okay?
Naoya?
Look. I'm conflicted.
If I win, then Kana's
gonna get punished.
If she gets killed,
it'd be on me.
Don't be ridiculous.
This is no time to worry
about someone else, okay?
Yeah, but--
Listen to me, you can't
afford to think about her.
I don't care about
this stupid game,
I'm not going to lose you!
Nobuaki.
[NOBUAKI] Please, you have to
vote for Naoya!
He's my closest friend.
I am begging you.
I'll never ask
for anything else.
Sure.
[KANA]
Misaki!
Come on. I'm trusting you
to do the right thing.
That means you have to write
my name on your ballot.
I mean, you and me,
we're friends, right?
[NOBUAKI] I don't want to let
Naoya die. Please, Misaki!
[KANA] I know you're on my side!
Aren't you, Misaki?
[NOBUAKI]
I'll do anything. Please!
[KANA]
Misaki, save me!
Stop it!
Don't ask me to do this.
I can't choose
between the two of them.
I can't. I can't do it.
Daisuke was our friend,
and I couldn't save him.
And now, I just couldn't
bear to lose Naoya.
It would break me.
Please, save my best friend.
-Misaki, let Naoya live.
-Nobuaki!
You're using Daisuke's death
to get an extra vote?
You're a coward!
[NAOYA]
No he's not!
He has more courage
than anyone here!
He's fighting desperately
to save my life.
He's down on his hands
and knees.
Where the hell do you get off
calling someone
like that a coward?
Naoya, I'll vote for you.
You were Daisuke's friend,
and it's thanks to him
I didn't get punished.
It seems right that
in his memory I should--
You're a little traitor!
Do you even understand
what you're saying right now?
You're basically telling me
you want me dead.
-No, that's not it.
-You're truly awful, Misaki.
I thought we were friends.
[KANA]
Damn it!
This isn't a joke.
And the last thing I'm going
to do is die for Naoya.
Damn this stupid game.
I'll win.
No matter what I have to do.
I'll come out on top!
[KANA]
Akira, please.
[AKIRA]
Seriously Kana?
[KANA]
I'm just so scared.
And if I lose, I'll never be
able to talk to you again.
Oh, Akira,
your hands are so warm.
Well, I am a man,
so I should protect you.
I'll make sure
nothing happens to you.
-You have my word.
-Thank you!
And after I win.
I'll do whatever you want me to.
[KANA]
I Promise.
[AKIRA]
Really? You mean anything?
[SHOUTA]
Hey man.
About Daisuke,
I'm sorry for what happened.
I can't believe he died
over what I thought
was some stupid joke,
and I'm-- I'm scared.
[SHOUTA]
I don't know what to do about
this whole popularity vote
thing, either.
No matter whose name I put down,
I'm killing someone!
And, I don't want to feel
like a murderer again!
You know?
So, then...
what the hell
am I supposed to do?
Well, for starters,
you could stop whining.
Daisuke's death was a tragedy,
but it wasn't all your fault.
If I'd been more careful,
then I would have been able
to save him myself.
-You don't know that.
-Sure.
Our one vote
might kill somebody,
but you have to think
of in it another way.
Your vote could also
save somebody.
I'm trying to save
my best friend.
That's all I want.
My only goal.
Listen to me.
I don't want to owe you
anything later,
so there's something
you should know.
Right now, the way
things are lookin',
your buddy's gonna lose.
[SHOUTA]
Kana's whoring herself out
to all the guys for their votes.
Like, legitimately.
She's already done it
with a bunch of them.
She's doing whatever it takes.
-Doing whatever they want.
-No way.
But there are lives
riding on this.
[SHOUTA]
No shit, hers is one of 'em.
Shingo,
you're going to vote
for Naoya, aren't you?
Yeah, obviously I'm going to.
Good to hear. I trust you.
Sure. I bet
he's got this in the bag.
You can definitely
count on my vote.
Can we?
Yeah, I've got your backs man,
we're friends after all.
Do you get it now?
He's in real trouble.
Well, I don't think
it'll make a difference,
but after what happened
with Daisuke, he's got my vote.
All right, now I'm going
to count the votes.
Naoya, Kana,
are you two ready?
For Kana. Kana.
Kana. Naoya! Kana.
-[NOBUAKI] Kana. Naoya. Naoya.
-[KANA] What a loser.
There's no point
in even counting.
[NOBUAKI]
Kana. Naoya.
[KANA]
No, no, that can't be right.
How are the numbers
so close together?
After all I did for this.
What the hell are you people
trying to pull?
If I lose, I die,
do they not get that?
-No. I'm going to win this.
-[NOBUAKI] Naoya.
I'll survive, I swear.
[NOBUAKI]
Naoya.
This is the last vote.
The name on this
decides who wins.
You ass.
I bet you're planning to cheat.
Give me that!
There's no way I'll lose.
My name has to be
written on this slip.
My name.
Ah! I win. [laughs]
I didn't need to worry.
There was no way he'd beat me
in a popularity contest.
Not so fast.
You didn't read all of it.
Huh?
This vote is for Naoya.
[KANA] You messed with the vote,
didn't you?
You cheated somehow!
[phones ringing]
No! I don't want to be
punished and killed.
I don't want to hang to death!
[Kana screams]
Kana!
[classmates gasp]
[chattering]
Oh!
[girl cries]
[phone rings]
Oh.
[Nobuaki cries]
[NAOYA]
Do you think
she's gonna make it?
[NOBUAKI]
Obviously it's really bad.
The doctors aren't sure
she's live through the night.
Man, I feel awful,
but I'd be dead
if it weren't for your help.
I don't even know
how to begin to thank you
for everything you've done.
Seriously man,
you're like my hero right now.
-No, I'm not a hero.
-Why?
Earlier,
I did something horrible
to make sure
that you would win the vote,
I pulled an evil trick.
[NAOYA]
What do you mean?
I sent this to people
who might vote for Kana
and fooled them
into putting your name.
[NAOYA] You said you had a way
to escape the King's Game?
I tricked them
into voting for you.
Dude, if they ever find out,
they're gonna go insane.
Yeah, they'll beat me up,
if not something even worse.
No. I won't let them.
You don't need
to worry about it.
The way I planned things,
I don't think there's that much
of a chance they'll attack me.
And why's that?
[NOBUAKI]
Like I said,
the trick I pulled
was especially bad.
Everyone who got
that message thinks
they were the only person
I was offering an escape to.
Plus, they had to respond
within five minutes.
Without any time
to think it through,
I knew they'd eventually
end up choosing
to betray Kana
in the end.
If they tell anyone,
they'll be accused of stabbing
their friend in the back,
not to mention abandoning
the rest of their classmates.
So there's no way
they can say anything.
That's why
the trick is so evil.
I made them drive
their friend to death
with a fake promise that
they'd be able to survive this.
-I'm nothing but a monster.
-No way!
You're not the one
to blame for this, Nobuaki.
The King is
the only monster.
-[gasps]
-You put yourself through
absolute hell to save
your best friend's life.
Do you really think
a monster would do that?
I don't know.
It's almost time for an order.
Maybe we'll luck out.
Maybe no message will come.
I don't think we're that lucky,
but whatever the King wants,
I promise that I'll protect
the both of you.
Nobuaki.
You guys are so cute together.
For real.
I'm kinda jealous, actually.
I feel like I'm never gonna
get a girl to like me.
[NOBUAKI]
What?
Where's all of this
suddenly coming from?
Don't worry.
You're such a good guy, Naoya.
I bet you'll get a girlfriend
better than me in no time.
Please, he wishes.
Naoya's not exactly good
at understanding girls.
[CHIEMI] I bet I know someone
who's even more clueless.
[NOBUAKI]
Who's that?
[beeping]
[flatline]
[phones ringing]
[NOBUAKI]
But why Naoya?
I get that Kana
couldn't obey her order,
but he shouldn't
have to do it.
Damn it! But it's ten
minutes to midnight!
What do we do?
Yeah, there's no way
I can complete the order.
[screams]
Do you have a plan?
[CHIEMI]
Wait. Nobuaki?
[NAOYA]
Where are you taking us?
Hey, what are you doing?
Open up!
Naoya!
Hurry up and carry out
the damn order!
I want you to survive.
No. You can't be serious.
Chiemi!
Please, do it.
You're the only one
who can save him now!
You're talking crazy!
I love both of you guys,
so I couldn't sleep
with her, ever!
I can't.
I'd be betraying both of you.
Please do it!
If you don't obey, you'll die.
Maybe I don't care
if I die, you idiot!
It'd be better than
hurting either of you.
Naoya, come on.
We don't have a choice here.
[CHIEMI]
If this is what it takes
to save your life,
so be it.
I'll be honest,
I don't wanna burn to death.
But, still--
I don't think I could
live with myself
if I betrayed the two of you!
You're betraying us now.
[NAOYA]
No. I'm not!
I'm begging you, dammit,
sleep with Chiemi!
I can't. There's no way!
[screams]
No. I won't.
Will you just let me die
with some honor?
But, why?
Please, hurry.
Do it while he's unconscious.
[cries]
[phone rings]
I'm sorry.
I'm the worst man alive.
No. I love you,
more than anything else
in this world.
That's why it hurt to do this.
I love you so much
that I could die right now!
[CHIEMI]
Please, promise me something.
No matter what,
promise me that there's no way
you'll die before I do.
Chiemi.
That's so sad.
Yeah.
Sure.
Maybe you did some
unforgivable things,
things you wish
you could take back.
That said,
you know what?
I still just can't see you
as a bad guy, not deep down.
Yeah, but I made
my best friend...
Most people couldn't
go that far.
Like you said,
you did it to save his life.
The King.
He's the one who's unforgivable.
You sound like...
You are not the one
to blame for this.
The King is the monster!
[KENTA]
Nobuaki,
you've lost a lot of people
who were important to you.
You've been through
so much intense pain.
I bet you can't even
put it into words,
But you are not alone.
You can lean on us.
I-- All I wanted to do
was to save everyone.
It's all gonna be okay.
When this is over, you'll be
crying tears of relief.
[NOBUAKI]
Sure. [cries]
[AIMI]
Natsuko.
What do you think
will happen now?
[NATSUKO]
If you don't want to die,
then all of you will do
exactly as I say, understand?
[phone rings]
[giggles]