♪
What in the hell is this place?
-[chiming]
-[gasps]
What's that?
[gasps]
-[rumbling]
-Huh?
[screams]
[GIRL]
Nobuaki. Nobuaki!
I want to live,
with you.
Stay with me, forever.
No!
Chiemi!
[gasps]
[screaming]
On your marks.
Get set.
[gun fires]
[ANNOUNCER]
The first group of relay runners
is off to a strong start.
Class Four leads,
followed by Class One!
And just like that,
batons have been passed off
to the second group!
[grunts, shrieks]
Uh-oh. Class One's runner
has taken quite a tumble!
We are so screwed.
I'm sorry, Nobuaki!
-[BOY] Nobuaki! Run!
-[GIRL] Come on, you can do it!
Go, Natsuko!
[giggles]
I've got this.
[NOBUAKI]
She's fast.
[ANNOUNCER]
Whoa! Class One's ace bolts past
Class Four's runner
to grab the lead!
Yeah, take 'em down, Natsuko!
You're doing amazing,
almost there!
[ANNOUNCER]
We have a winner!
Class One takes first place
in the inter-class relay!
[cheering]
Natsuko!
[BOY] Now we have more points
than Class Four.
[BOY 2] Yeah, if we keep it up,
we might win this thing!
[PHOTOGRAPHER]
Time for a group photo!
Please welcome Kanazawa,
our new transfer student.
It's a pleasure
to meet you all.
Your seat's in the last row,
next to the window.
Hmm?
Welcome to the back.
My name's Honda Natsuko.
-Nice to meet you.
-Honda?
Yup. So, where'd you
transfer in from?
Also, can I call you Nobu?
Hey. Look, Nobu.
What do you think, is this
a total masterpiece or what?
It's our teacher!
[sighs]
[chalk tapping blackboard]
[crying quietly]
So how come you moved
out here to the boonies?
Were there any hot girls
at your school?
Hey. Please tell me
you like soccer.
So, Kanazawa, were you
in any clubs or anything?
Will everyone please
just leave me alone.
Oh?
[students muttering]
Hey, come on, man.
Let's all be friends.
No!
I told you all
to leave me alone!
Hang on!
Where the heck are you going?
Just let him go.
You guys really
can't take a hint.
[birds singing]
[sighs]
Hi there, Nobu.
[giggles]
I skipped class too.
So, what's up?
Did something bad happen at
your old school that upset you?
Or is it... that you're just
afraid to make new friends.
[students chattering]
Hi, hi, Nobu!
How about you and me be partners
in the inter-class relay!
Yeah, thanks but no thanks.
You just don't get it, do you?
As far as we're concerned,
this sports festival is like
a big welcome party for you.
As the star of the day, you
gotta get out there and shine.
If you're gonna be
one of our runners,
I can cut your hair for you.
-[NOBUAKI] Uh...
-I guess he is a little shaggy.
Same goes for you, kid.
By the way, I'm our team's ace.
Yeah, Natsuko here
is insanely fast.
No matter what place we're in,
when I get that baton,
we are totally
taking home the gold!
[cheering]
-I can't.
-You'll be great, Nobu,
I'm sure of it. Come on.
You know what I like
about Natsuko?
She's always so happy.
Sure, but do you think
that's real?
She might be
covering up the fact
-that her parents were killed.
-Yeah, I heard about that.
-A plane crash, right?
-Uh-huh, but...
rumor is the whole thing
was a murder-suicide.
-Ugh.
-Either way, it's so sad.
[NOBUAKI]
What? Is that true?
Nobu, we're all hoping
that you'll get more comfortable
with our class.
[NOBUAKI]
Losing people close to you
is like losing
a piece of yourself.
I can't even
make friends anymore.
So how come she's able
to keep on smiling?
[cheering]
[NOBUAKI]
It's been a long time,
but I'm actually
having fun again.
Everyone seems to be grinning
and laughing constantly.
Things feel like they used to.
I'm starting to feel at home.
[clock ticking]
[ticking continuing]
-[chiming]
-[gasps]
No matter how much I hope
and pray, I can't escape.
But I already knew that.
I don't have any choice.
-Hey! Hey! Nobuaki!
-There he is!
-He's gonna do it?
-Kanazawa,
you must have gotten the same
text as the rest of us, right?
Or, wait, did you send it
'cause you've got
a thing for Natsuko?
No, it wasn't me.
[NOBUAKI] The order's
the same as last time,
and so are
the class's reactions.
Told you.
The guy's pissed 'cause
he's been put in the spotlight.
Oh, come on, it sounds
like an interesting game!
If you don't kiss,
you get punished,
but, like, by who, huh?
This is so dumb.
Natsuko, you know you don't
have to kiss this boy.
Well, I wouldn't mind,
just once?
[gasps]
[laughter]
I need you to listen to me!
The King's Game
is very, very real.
We're gonna start getting
a bunch of orders!
Even if you try to run,
you can't escape it.
But, please,
no one freak out yet.
If you all will just trust me,
we can confront
this thing together.
[laughing]
Damn, Kanazawa.
Didn't know you had
such a weird sense of humor.
-I'm not joking!
-That's kinda creepy.
Just come out with it.
You wanna to kiss Natsuko,
don't ya?
No! The game is real!
You only get 24 hours.
And if you don't do what
you're told, you're punished!
You could even die!
You've got to believe me!
You hear that?
None of us are laughing anymore.
If I were you,
I'd go back to being quiet.
-You guys.
-What a freak.
And we tried to be so nice.
-What was that all about?
-I've got no idea.
Everybody,
you should be in your seats.
Don't be such a troll.
Got it?
[NOBUAKI]
Nobody will believe me
if I try to explain it
without any proof.
I don't blame them.
We didn't really believe it
until people started dying.
We thought it was a joke.
Oh, there you are!
[panting]
That was a pretty dumb way
of telling her you like her.
But if you really have
a thing for Natsuko,
then I can give you some help.
Just don't make me regret it.
Because the thing is,
I happen to know that
she's interested in you too.
So, here's the deal.
I'm gonna give you her phone
number so you can call her.
-Can you please get outta here?
-Huh?
I'm sorry.
-I was being weird earlier.
-What's with you?
Is that how you treat someone
who's trying to do you a favor?
-Please, just leave me alone!
-You are such a pain.
[sighs]
[NOBUAKI] If I don't obey
the order, then I'm gonna die.
But I don't wanna drag
Natsuko down with me.
There's really no hope
for either of us, anyway.
If we're all gonna die,
it might be better to go first.
It's almost been 24 hours.
I guess that's the end
for us both.
[panting]
Wow. The stars
are gorgeous tonight.
But you'll miss them
if you keep your head down.
-Natsuko?
-I've been looking everywhere.
I'm so glad I found you.
Aimi said you were
acting kinda strange
when she talked to you today.
Are you worried about
what happened in class?
Or is it something else,
did I do something wrong?
[chiming]
-Please just go.
-But we've barely talked.
And what about
the King's orders?
You said it was real,
so shouldn't we think
about what--
I can't kiss you!
Sorry.
Is it 'cause you've got
your eye on someone else?
Yeah. There's a girl
who I will never forget.
Oh, an old girlfriend?
Was it a bad breakup?
How'd it go down?
It might help you
to talk about it.
I guess we're long-distance now.
She's gone far away.
This might sound kinda weird.
But have you ever thought
about what heaven is like?
Actually, I don't believe
that heaven is real.
What matters the most
is the here and now,
the actions we perform
while we're still alive.
Hey. What are you doing?
It's cool, I'm totally fine.
Thanks for the catch.
[chiming]
A text from the king.
Sixty seconds remaining.
-No, please get away from me.
-Listen,
I don't know what happened
with that girl or anything,
but maybe I can help you
work your way through it.
Trust me, there's nothing
you can do to help.
You're lying. Otherwise,
you wouldn't be crying.
From day one, I liked you.
I'd really love it
if you went out with me.
Our time is almost over now.
So, would it be okay
if I kissed you?
No!
-You're seriously saying no?
-I am.
Your girlfriend
is really lucky, I'm jealous.
[chiming]
Must be him.
That means it's time
for our punishment.
[NOBUAKI]
Her lips are so cold.
I'm not the type
who gives up easily.
-What?
-Consider that kiss a challenge
for your long-distance
girlfriend.
[NOBUAKI]
She's so happy, and kind.
The whole class loves her.
She hasn't done
a single thing wrong.
-I'm so sorry about this.
-It's okay.
But your words and actions
don't match up at all.
What's with you?
[chiming]
Do you feel anything weird
starting to happen to you?
Well, my heart's
definitely pounding hard.
[NOBUAKI] Why am I getting
so many texts right now?
The punishment should
have already started.
I screwed up.
I assumed the text from Aimi
was the punishment message.
We must have kissed
before midnight.
So, that means
the other texts...
Deep rest? So does that mean?
Natsuko, you have to call
every classmate you can
and tell them
not to go to sleep!
-Why, what's going on?
-Just hurry up and do it!
[chiming]
Damn it!
It's happening.
The two of them
must've been asleep already.
-Nobu, what's wrong?
-Natsuko.
Which of our classmates
lives closest to where we are?
I think, Furusawa Tsubasa
is around here?
He lives at the block
four intersection.
All right, then.
I'm heading to Tsubasa's house.
Remember, call every
classmate you can,
tell them they have to
stay awake no matter what.
And have everyone meet up
somewhere together.
Nobu, you're scaring me.
-I don't understand what--
-Please help.
Right now, you're the only
person I can count on.
Nobu!
Come on, please, you gotta
open the door right now!
What do you want?
You get your ass back here now!
I've got you.
Hon, call the police!
Damn it! Let go!
Tsubasa!
Tsubasa, what are...?
What's happening?
Quick, somebody call
an ambulance!
Now, or he's not
gonna make it!
[FATHER]
No! Tsubasa!
[panting]
[chiming]
I was too late.
And now all of
those kids are dead.
[murmuring]
[GIRL] This is so stupid.
Why the hell are we out here?
-I'm tired.
-Yeah, me, too.
-So lame.
-Who all are we missing?
Couple of people.
[GIRL] I don't even know
what's going on.
[panting]
Hey! I need everyone to stay
calm and listen to me closely.
God. What the hell's been up
with you the last few days?
First the kiss, and now these
hangings, it's not funny.
-No. It's true!
-Explain something to me.
Why won't the guy who's joking
about our classmates dying
answer his damn phone?
[murmuring]
Um. I have bad news.
[sobbing]
When I was on my way over here,
I stopped by Nanami's house.
And she-- I found her dead.
She was hanging in her room.
-What, no! You can't be serious.
-It could be a serial killer!
You're wrong. It's not a person
that's doing this!
How long are you gonna keep
saying this crap, you idiot?
Our friends are dying.
All I'm doing
is telling the truth.
And how do you know all this?
Because...
this is not the first time
that my class has played
the King's Game.
[gasping]
[whimpering]
Okay, so explain it to us.
What happened the last time
you played the King's Game?
-It's your fault.
-What did you get us all into?
Start talking.
Tell us everything you know.
My classmates died.
Only I survived.
[gasping, murmuring]
This is not the kind of thing
that I would joke about!
We didn't believe this nightmare
was real at first, either,
but then it started,
and we couldn't stop it.
One by one, my friends all died.
So, if we disobey the king's
orders, we're dead, too?
But Natsuko said that
you refused to kiss her!
-You knew about the punishments.
-I did.
Then when you turned her down,
you basically tried to kill her!
[gasps]
I don't really care
if you have a death wish,
but you were going to get
her killed along with you!
-Aimi--
-Don't you dare take his side.
If it's true, I'll never
forgive this creep.
It's true.
Murazumi's right about me.
-[MURAZUMI] You're disgusting.
-[BOY] What a piece of shit!
-Murderer!
-Scum!
-Hit him.
-Murderer!
-Kick his ass!
-You're sick!
-I'm so sorry!
-Shut your mouth!
Screw this King's Game!
You and whoever else
is behind this
can both go straight to hell.
-Stop, it! We have to stay calm!
-Natsuko.
You realize this guy
almost got you murdered, right?
-I don't think that.
-Hey.
Who here thinks he's the one
sending all these creepy texts?
[GIRL]
It's gotta be him!
[BOY] I'll bet he's the one
killing people.
-Wait! I don't--
-Shut up!
[screams]
No, let me go.
I'm just trying to help
everyone! Please stop--
We've heard
just about everything
we need to from you,
you bastard.
You're nothing
but a damn murderer.
-Hey, look at this.
-Huh?
Yuuichi, it says
you got a punishment.
[gasps]
[retches]
What the hell?
What'd you do to me?
Nothing, it wasn't me!
[grunting]
[screaming]
Help... me.
[whimpering]
[sobbing]
[NOBUAKI]
There's no stopping it.
A new King's Game has begun.