[RIA] I'm honestly impressed
you didn't cry.
Ria.
I mean, not that I'd care
if you were murdered.
But since you're still alive,
you can tell me something.
I don't have anything
to say to you.
Yousuke was
researching the game.
I want to know
what he found out.
I switched my number over.
Do you think it'll be okay?
Yeah, as long as you can still
get texts from the King,
he has no reason to punish you.
Well now that
that's out of the way.
We should probably head out
to Yonaki Village.
Right.
[KENTA] This story's so crazy
and hard to believe.
But it's all true?
Yeah.
I can't imagine
how painful that was.
I only made it through
because Chiemi was there.
She meant
the entire world to me.
She was your rock
through it all, huh?
Things probably got even worse
in your last game,
but will you tell us about it?
If it's something
that could happen to us,
we need to be prepared for it.
Yeah, sure. You should know
how bad this could get.
[OPERATOR]
The phone you have dialed
is out of the service area
or is no longer in service.
Please make sure
you have the correct number,
and then try again later.
Damn!
Come on, man.
You better be okay.
-[phone ringing]
-Huh?
Hey, Nobuaki, is that you?
[ABE]
Huh?
No stupid. It's me, Toshiyuki.
[NAOYA]
Uh, what is it?
We need to figure out what we
should do about today's order.
[NAOYA]
Uh, well... I don't know.
If we screw this up,
every single one of us
is gonna end up dead!
I know it's called a game,
but this new command
is freakin' ridiculous.
You saw it right?
One of us has to roll a die,
and then name
that amount of people.
Then everyone
who gets called out
is punished along with the
poor bastard that has to roll!
I mean, what the hell?
And if we don't play along,
we're still screwed! Argh!
I wanna kill this psycho!
So, what's the plan, smart guy?
Who the hell is gonna roll?
[NAOYA]
Um, maybe--
If Nobuaki were here,
I bet he'd know what to do.
Just give me some time to think.
[line clicks]
Huh?
I don't care what we have to do.
You and I are gonna survive.
Yeah, definitely.
There are only ten
of us left alive.
Worst case scenario,
someone rolls a six,
which means only three of us end
up making it through the night.
Those are some
really crappy odds.
And whoever rolls,
picks who dies.
I can't let Chia do it.
Not only is she a real bitch,
she totally hates me, too.
I bet she'd pull every dirty
trick imaginable to win this.
I'm not able to talk
to Nobuaki right now,
but I know he'd want me
to protect Chiemi.
[phone chimes]
The park?
Yeah, of course.
Sure. I understand.
Thanks for letting me know.
Please send her my best.
Masami.
She's in the hospital.
Tried to kill herself
and slit her wrists.
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
Hey!
Why the hell haven't
Nobuaki and Ria shown up?
We have a decision
to make here, dammit.
Come on, which of you guys
is gonna roll the die?
It's like Nobuaki said,
we need to trust each other
and work together
if we really want
to take down the King.
I agree with her.
Huh?
If we put our brains together,
maybe we can end this.
But we all have to believe
in each other.
Sure, great idea, Keita,
That's what we'll do. No sweat.
So, then.
Why don't you go ahead and roll?
Come on, I believe in you.
I don't know why
you're in such a hurry.
You know everybody in class
hates you, right?
I mean, your little pet over
there might save you.
Not because he likes you,
because he's terrified of you,
But the rest of us
are sure to name you first
if we're the one to roll.
Say what?
No one cares what you think!
'Cause you're the one everyone
hates, you ugly whore.
What? I'm the ugly one?
You look like a boxer that's
taken too many to the face.
I should kill you myself,
you cow!
-Stop it, guys.
-[ALL gasp]
Wait. Is that him?
You're okay!
Thank goodness!
Chiemi!
Sorry, I hope
you weren't worried.
I was fine.
I promise.
I knew you were out there
trying to help us.
All right, Ria, what gives?
You called us out here,
so where do you get off
being the late one?
Fool.
[scoffs] Whatever.
The more people who are here,
the less likely I am
to have to roll this damn thing
or get my name called.
-How can you say that?
-Come on, man.
You know deep down inside
you're just as relieved as I am.
Don't be an idiot!
You're the one being stupid!
-Quit it!
-Ha! Hey, don't blame me,
your buddy here is the one
who threw the first punch.
Will you knock it off?
What the hell is wrong
with you tonight?
I've just got way too much stuff
I wanna do in my life
to die right now.
I am not gonna let
this game kill me!
But if we work together,
then maybe we can--
Hey, listen, man.
We're best friends, aren't we?
-Yeah.
-Then I'm begging you.
If you roll the die right now,
you can save me.
Are you serious?
If anybody other than you rolls,
I know they're gonna
call my name first.
You're the only one who can keep
me from being punished here.
[CHIA]
Pathetic.
You see what we're
dealing with now, don't you?
He's an ass who didn't even
give a second thought
about sacrificing
his best friend
just so he has
a chance to win this.
I don't wanna die!
Dammit, screw whoever's
putting us through this!
No, don't do it!
I can't stand it.
It's turning my best friend
into a monster.
Why the hell did he have
to get in the way?
Just one more second
and it would've been over.
Heh, you've shown us
who you really are.
You're gonna be the first person
named no matter who rolls now.
Ha! Serves him right.
[growls]
Ah! No!
Stop it! Don't touch me!
Let her go!
Let go!
-What are you doing? Hold still.
-Please!
If you don't shut up and stop
struggling, I'll stab you.
-[MINAKO] Stop it!
-No, don't!
No one move
or I swear I'll kill her!
Oh, please, don't be stupid.
We all know you're way
too much of a coward
to actually
go through with this.
You just watch me!
[screams]
[laughs]
Chiemi!
I told you
not to move, loverboy!
Listen up,
I'm the one who's giving
the orders from now on,
not the King.
So. If you try anything
I'll kill her.
I am not playing
around here! Got it?
Now let's get started.
Nobuaki, Naoya.
I want one of you
to roll the die.
If I'm the one who does this,
I'll be punished.
But if I don't,
he's gonna hurt Chiemi.
[NOBUAKI]
I'll do it.
Just get your hands off her!
You don't have to!
Ha! I'm not letting her go
until this is over.
So hurry up
and get on with it.
It's all right.
Give the die to me.
-What are you doing?
-We need you to stay alive.
To protect Chiemi.
And I know you can
take down the King.
You two are the reason
I'm still here.
So if this means
you'll both survive,
then I'm happy
to roll the die, really.
Don't do it, Naoya!
[laughs]
[phone beeping]
It says I have ten minutes
to pick the number
of classmates that I rolled.
So that's six of them.
If I say their name,
they'll be punished.
Hurry up. Pick anyone,
just as long as it's not me.
I'd recommend Chia or Minako.
Hell, you could even say
Chiemi's name for all I care.
Naoya, um, name Masami.
She isn't here
and she tried to kill herself.
Dammit, it's not that simple.
People's lives are
in my hands, Keita!
-[phones ringing]
-[ALL gasp]
No. Me?
Oh, my God.
I can't say any names at all.
But I was just trying to help.
Not me. [crying]
I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to, I promise,
it was an accident, I swear.
You idiot!
My neck hurts.
[groaning]
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
Hey. It's fixed.
Right?
Oh no!
[screams]
Oh, my god.
Things had
gotten so extreme.
So many of us had died.
Our friendships had all been
pushed to the limits.
But still,
whatever was behind it
all wasn't satisfied.
[gasps]
[coughs]
Masami, the girl
in the hospital,
was the next to be named.
Naoya eventually gave in
to Toshiyuki's threats.
He called out Chia and Minako.
They died in front of us.
And Naoya still had to name
two more people.
Otherwise, we'd all be punished.
We're running out of time.
-Say Nobuaki next!
-Naoya!
Please, you have to say
my name instead, not his.
Punish me. It's okay.
Don't listen to her.
Say my name.
Save Chiemi no matter what.
I can't kill you.
[shouts]
[thud]
You, too? Traitor.
Open your eyes already, moron!
Do you even understand
what you're doing to us?
I don't think you get it.
We have to look out
for ourselves in this.
I can't take it anymore.
Naoya, you have to call
my name next and then his.
Do it. End this right now!
Naoya! Name us!
Are you sure?
Don't you dare!
If you say it, I'll murder you.
Abe Toshiyuki.
Fujioka Toshiyuki.
[phones ringing]
Chiemi. Are you okay?
Nobuaki, I hate this!
He needs you right now
so go be with him.
Tell me what can I do.
It's too late for me.
I'm gonna die next.
But, you know what?
At least if I have to die,
I got to do it saving
the two of you.
I'm honestly glad.
What's happening?
My arm, it-- it hurts.
It hurts!
[screams]
No!
Thanks for always
being there for me.
I love you both so much.
I want you to survive.
Destroy the king.
You have to.
I know you can.
I believe in you.
[screams]
You can't!
No! No, Naoya.
Talk to me! Naoya!
Hey, Nobuaki.
Let me ask you something.
What do you think heaven's like?
Must be an amazing place, yeah?
[NAOYA]
Because everyone stays there.
Nobody ever comes back.
Naoya? Don't go.
Naoya! [cries]
[phone chimes]
Stop it.
What do you think you're doing?
I thought that'd be obvious.
I'm going to take down
the King right now.
There won't be any more orders.
Mm. Is that really possible?
Since the first text,
I've been looking
into the King's Game,
but I couldn't find out
everything on my own.
Luckily, I was able to get
closer to what's behind this,
--by adding what Yousuke
sent you to my own research.
It started over
30 years ago.
There was a series
of unexplainable deaths
in a place called
Yonaki Village.
I think that was
the very first King's Game.
It was before cell phones,
obviously,
so the orders were delivered
to the players on paper,
all signed by the King.
Pretty soon the villagers
started dropping like flies.
No one could understand why.
You can imagine
this caused an uproar.
But the police
and the public officials
couldn't figure out
how to stop it.
Afterwards, though,
some scientists theorized
that the game might not have
been started by a person,
but a virus.
A virus?
Yes, they believed
the mysterious deaths
were actually caused
by a virus
that sent powerful suggestions
to people's brains.
I don't understand.
What are you saying?
Hypnotized people can injure
themselves with just a thought.
They can make lesions
appear on their skin
without ever being touched.
You see,
when the human body receives
a powerful enough cue
or suggestion,
it can actually
destroy its own cells.
It's likely the King's Game
takes this phenomenon
to the extreme.
Hold on a second.
If that's true, how did we get
this "virus" in the first place?
It's not like it came
from a text message?
According to at least
one theory,
the suggestions are like
a type of infectious disease
that can spread.
The virus born in Yonaki Village
was never eradicated.
As communication networks
and the internet evolved,
it began to move
through them freely.
It, too, grew and changed.
To this day,
the virus continues to spread
through our cell phones.
Wait, is that even possible?
Another thing,
everyone who's killed
in the game receives
a one-syllable
text from the King
right before they get punished.
Unfortunately, I wasn't able
to form any kind of sentence
that made sense
based on the texts
that Yousuke and I compiled.
But I was able to complete
an anti-virus
that should eradicate
the King's Game.
I found a fatal bug
hidden in its programming.
With a few keystrokes,
I can get rid of every trace
of it on the network.
Ria, who are you, exactly?
My father was smart.
A genius when it came
to computer programming.
But...
that doesn't matter, really.
I'm starting the program.
The King's Game virus
has been deleted.
Feels kind of anticlimactic.
Is it really over?
-[computer beeps]
-[ALL gasp]
[NOBUAKI]
Oh god. No!
I see.
So the bug itself
was a trap set by the King.
Ria!
Well, I hate to admit it,
but it looks like
I'm not gonna be the winner
of the King's Game after all.
Ria.
I'm sure you've heard
the rumors about me, right?
That I was abused
by the father I once
looked up to more than anything.
Practically every day of my life
was a living hell.
At least until
he finally killed himself.
For a while, I was sure
I'd lost the will to live.
But this game made me
feel something again.
I'd been drifting
through life aimlessly.
But then, suddenly,
the King's Game
gave me a purpose.
Ria!
It's not that I wanted
to keep living,
not entirely.
I just wanted to win is all.
Because there's no point in
playing a game unless you win.
Nobuaki, you were my insurance.
Understand?
Just in case I didn't
manage to survive.
Nobuaki, Chiemi, the two of you
have to finish off
this bastard King in my place.
[BOTH]
Ria!
I see something,
you think that's it?
After all this time,
I'm finally here.
Yonaki Village.