You think that's it?
[bird shrieking]
[NOBUAKI] After all this time,
I'm finally here.
Yonaki Village.
We can squeeze
through that hole.
[footsteps]
[KENTA]
No signal.
That's so loud. What is it?
Nothing, just the wind.
This isn't good.
What's wrong?
Mizuki still has
to send two texts
telling people to die tonight.
So what are we gonna do?
We should have her send
the texts to Natsuko and Haruka.
Uh?
[NOBUAKI]
Natsuko's been acting crazy,
so she's bound
to become a problem.
Haruka's order was to let
Tsubasa touch her chest,
but...
Well, he's already dead,
so that's impossible.
Haruka can't be saved.
It makes the most sense
to choose those two.
At least that way
we can save Mizuki.
I know things have gone crazy.
But who are we to say
whose life matters most?
So you don't think
a baby deserves
to live more
than a dying old person?
A life is a life, Nobuaki.
If you keep thinking that way,
you won't make it out of this.
-[MIZUKI] Hey, guys.
-[BOTH] Uh?
[MIZUKI]
I think we're here.
I can see something
on the other side of the tunnel.
This is it.
I wonder how long it's been
since anyone set foot
in this place.
The locals must know
this village is cursed.
[wind howling]
[cawing]
Wait. Why is it
so dark out here?
I mean, the sun
should still be out.
Whoa.
[KENTA]
This is the place, right?
[NOBUAKI]
Yeah.
It's Yonaki Village
[cawing]
Okay. So, uh,
what should we check out first?
I don't know,
but there must be a clue
about the King's Game
here somewhere.
Honda?
Hey, wait, Nobuaki!
You sure it's okay to go in?
I have to look.
If anything weird happens,
just yell.
Mizuki and I'll watch
things out here.
Uh?
Is that Chiemi and her father?
What in the hell is this place?
This looks just like them,
but how can that be?
[NOBUAKI] "I'm coming
to apologize to you, Chiemi."
What the hell does that mean?
Is her dad connected
to the game?
[KENTA]
Mizuki? Where'd you go?
Hey, Mizuki!
Where are you? Can you hear me?
[KENTA]
I'm such an idiot.
I was too distracted
by that house.
[phone beeps]
Hold on.
A text?
But I shouldn't have
a signal way out here.
No. The King killed
seven people all at once?
You bastard!
Screw your punishments!
You won't get away with it!
Do you hear me!
What do I do?
Go back and regroup
with Nobuaki?
But what if Mizuki needs me?
Think. Come on!
Who's there?
Mizuki.
I just came back
to say goodbye.
Hey, guys.
Where'd you go?
What is this?
[flies buzzing]
Oh, my god!
The man looks
a lot younger here,
but I think this is
Chiemi's dad.
Okay.
So did he kill himself
or what?
But why?
What was he apologizing for?
Is it because he dragged
Chiemi into the game?
Or maybe he was part
of the very first one
that ended up
destroying this village.
And then when it started
happening to Chiemi.
He might have thought
it was his fault,
and then committed suicide
because of his guilt
or something.
Wait. "Daughters"?
Chiemi had a sister?
Natsuko?
Wait, what? They're related?
-No way.
-Welcome to the back.
My name's Honda Natsuko.
Nice to meet you.
And here I was hoping you'd have
some sort of good advice
since you played this
stupid game before and survived.
[NOBUAKI] If Chiemi
and Natusko are sisters, then...
Ugh!
Could you be more annoying?
Face it.
Every animal puts its own
survival above everything else.
You can't hesitate or be afraid
to betray your closest friend
to save yourself.
You know that.
After all, you survived, right?
Who'd you kill?
Does that mean...
Natsuko survived
a King's Game before, too?
What in the world
are you talking about?
There's no need for you
to say goodbye.
I hear that love found
during a tragedy
won't lead to anything.
It just disappears,
like a dream.
I figured out what to do
with my order.
Did you know that it's possible
to send a text to yourself?
I really want
to protect you, Kenta.
I don't want to hurt anyone,
so I'll message myself
and send the other text
to Natsuko.
I really don't trust her.
She was acting suspicious
back at the park.
And then she...
She tried to force me
to murder you!
[KENTA]
Mizuki. Please, don't.
Listen, Kenta.
I know it's not for real.
But, um, will you call me cute?
Or tell me you think
I'm beautiful?
It'd mean a lot to me.
What are you talking about?
You can't just ask me
to say that.
And you probably don't wanna
lie to me, do you?
Never mind.
I always did like
your honesty, Kenta.
And... Well, actually,
I like everything about you.
Is it possible that you might
feel the same way about me?
Uh, well, I... I guess.
I can't say it!
[sobbing]
Stupid me.
I just had to go
and make things awkward.
I'm sorry. Goodbye!
-Wait!
-[MIZUKI crying]
[KENTA] You didn't give me
a chance to answer you!
[MIZUKI]
You didn't have to say anything.
I've said what I wanted.
Let's just leave it at that.
Please forgive me
for being so selfish!
Don't. You can't stop me.
It's late.
I have to find a signal
so I can send these texts.
Let me go!
Not yet. Stay.
[MIZUKI] It's not fair
to hold me like that.
You're stronger than me.
Don't make me scream for help.
[KENTA] But what if the love
found in this tragedy
could actually last?
What do you mean by that?
You better not be
playing around with me,
or I'll take it the wrong way.
Let me show you.
I'm so happy.
Kenta. I love you.
And now I can tell you
what I really want to happen.
Okay?
Yeah, of course.
I want you to die
with me, Kenta.
This game has nothing
but pain ahead for us.
But I can make sure
that you and I
never have to suffer again.
You don't mean...
[MIZUKI]
You have to remember.
If I die, then you die, too.
No matter what,
you'll follow me in death.
We'll go together hand-in-hand.
No. Hold on.
I can't think of anything
more romantic.
Right?
It's just so perfect!
What you're saying is crazy.
Snap out of it!
If we die together,
then our love will be eternal
and nothing will break us apart.
You're wrong, Mizuki.
I won't let either of us die.
You're not yourself.
Kenta.
If you feel the same way
I do about you,
then show me.
[KENTA] That isn't the way
to prove my feelings.
If you die, then everything
we've gone through
will have been for nothing.
No, that's not true.
[KENTA]
This would all be over.
No more happiness.
You only get to have
the lasting love
if you're alive,
don't you get that?
Open your eyes!
[MIZUKI] I'd hoped my feelings
would get through to you.
But you don't understand.
I have to go.
I'll find a place
with a signal.
Then I'll send the "die" texts
to myself and Natsuko.
-No.
-I love you.
-Goodbye
-Wait. Don't go!
[BOTH grunt]
I'm sorry.
But it's for the best.
A few minutes to spare.
[KENTA] There, that should count
as Mizuki sending the text.
You've gotta live
for the both of us now.
Don't get any more crazy ideas
just because I'm gone.
[phone beeps]
Two new messages.
The one from Mizuki.
And one from the King.
Obedience confirmed.
Maybe that means
I followed through
on the order I gave myself
to protect Mizuki.
All right then.
You're going to be okay.
Nobuaki will be upset.
But I hope he'll understand
why I did this.
It's all up to him now.
[NOBUAKI]
I have to find them
and get out of this village
before midnight.
That light.
Is that a cell tower?
[KENTA]
No signal.
I bet they went there
so Mizuki could get a signal
for her phone.
So she could text Natsuko--
and Haruka.
Unless...
But who are we to say
whose life matters most?
He wouldn't, would he?
Damn it.
Don't you dare, Kenta!
[crying softly]
Tsubasa. Why did you have
to go get punished?
Why didn't you just grope me
like the stupid
King's order said?
[phone beeps]
Huh?
-[screams]
-[phone screen shatters]
[CHOCO whines]
[KURAMOTO]
I've gotten rid of everything
important to me.
Except you.
[whining continues]
[growling]
I can't!
[CHOCO panting]
Not you, Choco!
You're the one thing
in this world
I could never stand to hurt!
[crying]
[running footsteps]
[panting]
Kenta!
You found us.
Who?
Who did they go to?
[phone chimes]
Sixty seconds remaining.
[KENTA]
That can't be right.
I used her fingers
to send messages
to me and Natsuko.
Nothing's happen to me yet.
You don't think...
What?
Natsuko said that sending texts
from a difference device
wouldn't be the same.
That Mizuki was as good as dead
when she broke her phone.
I thought she was lying.
Trying to scare us or something.
I guess not. Crap.
Well, I feel bad for Mizuki.
But at least you'll survive--
I'll send it to myself.
Saying protect Yukimura Mizuki.
Save her.
Make sure that
she survives this.
Sounds like you've put it
together, too, huh?
I ordered myself
to keep Mizuki safe.
But I wasn't able
to protect her.
And now I'm going to die
because I couldn't do it.
Damn it. This can't be.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't supposed
to be this way.
I failed.
Why does everyone
I care about end up dying?
Turn around.
Let me see your face.
I don't think I can look you
in the eye right now.
You idiot.
-I'm sorry!
-Don't, I'm okay.
Listen to me.
I think you're the most
amazing person I know.
You tried to help her.
Not everyone would put
their life on the line
to save someone else.
That doesn't matter anymore.
How is Mizuki?
Has she gotten a punishment yet?
Please. Go.
Leave me alone with her.
Kenta!
Get up.
Crawl to her.
You can't let this stop you.
[NOBUAKI]
Let me help you!
Leave us!
You still have work
you need to do.
All of this will pay off
in the end, right?
Sorry that I can't
stick around to help you.
Go on, get outta here.
Mizuki, I'm coming.
[sobbing softly]
[KENTA] I'm sorry.
I couldn't keep my promise.
Dammit. Gotta stay awake. Uh.
[MIZUKI moans]
Kenta. You're here?
No. Why'd she have
to wake up right now?
Kenta!
[KENTA]
She's just going to suffer.
Hold on.
Yeah, take 'em down, Natsuko!
You're doing amazing,
almost there!
How does that sound?
If I don't follow the order,
I'll die, too.
So you know I'll do
everything to protect you.
Mizuki.
You must've been so scared.
Thanks for coming
all the way out here with us.
Kenta. My friend.
You gave me hope.
I learned so much from you both.
Seriously.
But I still want
to know one thing.
Tell me, Kenta.
Was the sacrifice
you made worth it?
[phone ringing]
Who has my phone?
[NATSUKO]
Hi there, Nobu, babe!
So, are Kenta and Mizuki
still alive?
Or did they die in front of you?
Natsuko!