Ria?
Nami didn't get death
assigned as her punishment.
She killed herself
of her own free will.
Uh!
Is that what you
came here to say?
Oh, scary.
You could use some
of that anger,
to try and murder me.
[RIA]
Do you think you could do it?
Remember,
I did tell you
that I'm the King.
If you kill me,
this whole game is over.
[NOBUAKI]
You shut up.
We know The King
isn't in our class
because Nami sacrificed herself
to figure that out.
Are you sure about that?
You were there,
so you saw
that she didn't touch me.
I grabbed her hand
and was in control.
So that means
technically speaking,
she didn't grab me herself.
No. You're trying to confuse me.
Wasn't it you who said you were
sure the King was in our class?
Were you really that wrong?
[NOBUAKI] If she really is
the King, then...
I could end her right now.
And the game
would finally be over.
Ria!
[panting]
If I find out that
you're really behind this game,
I swear that
I'll kill you myself.
God, you're a joke.
This is getting so boring.
See? If I were the King,
then you'd be dead right now.
You can never
let your guard down.
You've gotta be more
committed than that.
Do you actually think
you can beat him
with such a weak attitude?
Yeah, okay, I get it.
You're not The King
so what the hell
are you trying to do right now?
I guess if we're being honest,
I just want to have fun
playing the game.
And a game's only enjoyable
if you win, don't you think?
How could you say
something like that?
This monster wants
to murder all of us.
Which means I'll do
whatever it takes
to make sure I'm the winner.
I'll even kill you.
As long as I live.
What the hell?
Have you gone totally insane
or something?
There must be another way.
Somehow we can
get out of this game
without any other
classmates dying.
Maybe. I guess
there's no real harm
in trying to play the game
your way.
For now.
I still think you're going
to lose to the King
and end up dead, though.
But that doesn't matter, since
either way I'll come out on top.
Yousuke.
Yeah? What is it?
I'm just thinking about how long
this game has been going on.
Mm.
[KAORI]
If it doesn't stop,
am I going to die, too?
Kaori.
It's gonna be okay.
I'll end it.
I've been doing some research
into the game's history.
Along with all the deaths
that have occurred.
I'll find a way
to stop this curse.
Kaori.
You are not gonna to die.
I promise you.
Thanks for saying that.
Hey, there's no need to cry.
You just have to trust me, okay?
-You know what?
-Uh.
This kinda reminds me
of when we were kids.
Like when we were
in elementary school.
The older boys would pick on me,
but you had my back.
You stood up for me,
-and made sure I was safe.
-Hm.
I guess you've always
been there for me,
-my whole life.
-Really?
You should give me
your phone number.
So we can check on each other
through all this.
Yeah, okay. Sounds good.
It's weird to admit,
but I probably
would have been too shy
to ask for your number
before the game.
Heh, I get that.
Thank you.
I feel better,
like things'll end up
all right. See ya.
Please be careful.
Our classmates just keep dying.
Three more last night.
Shingo and Motoki
got into a fight,
and Shingo ended up
falling down some stairs.
Motoki died from some
kind of weird seizure
and it sounds like Maki died
from the same thing.
Akemi apparently
picked Motoki and Maki
to send her texts out to.
[NAOYA]
Are you listening?
You look spaced.
[NAOYA]
Who's is this?
[NOBUAKI]
It's Nami's.
She's dead.
Everyone keeps dying.
Sometimes right in front
of their friends.
I don't think that I can
take it much longer.
Nobuaki.
-[phone ringing]
-Uh.
-Hello?
-[YOUSUKE] Nobuaki.
It's me.
-Yousuke?
-Listen to this.
I'm researching the King's Game
and I think I found something.
It could be a clue
as to how this is happening.
-Seriously?
-Here's the thing:
everyone who's dead
because of the game
got a text from the King
right before they died.
-He messaged the victims?
-Yeah.
It was just a single syllable
for each, though.
Okay, so what does that mean?
[YOUSUKE]
Honestly, I'm not sure yet.
But it could lead us
to something else.
A way to stop this.
Hey man, look here.
Wait a sec.
Nami got one, too.
It just says "R-E",
but it's from the King.
That's a big help, thanks.
We all need to work together
to end this thing.
If we do, we can save
as many people as possible.
You're right.
Kinda gives me hope.
But there is something else,
something that feels
really wrong to me.
[YOUSUKE]
What is it?
The way Ria's acting.
She called herself the King.
And she seems to know more
about the game than anyone else.
Plus,
it's practically impossible
to tell what she's thinking.
Ria, huh?
Do we even know
who she really is?
[YOUSUKE]
Well, I've heard some rumors.
Apparently she hasn't
always been so closed off.
She used to smile all the time,
and was actually friendly.
A totally different girl.
-Yeah?
-Uh huh.
[YOUSUKE]
But then her biological father,
he started abusing her,
sexually.
And after that,
she just kind of shut down
and stopped showing emotions
or opening up to anyone.
That's terrible.
I think she's been
acting strange, too, though.
If I find anything out,
I'll tell you.
Thanks.
[YOUSUKE] Also, can I ask you
to do something?
[NOBUAKI]
Sure, whatever you need.
[YOUSUKE]
It's about Kaori.
If I end up
not making it through this...
will you take care of her?
For me?
Course I will. Promise.
Don't worry.
I'll do whatever I can
to protect her.
[YOUSUKE]
Thanks. We'll talk soon.
Sure thing. Be careful.
[phones chime]
"Unnecessary"?
What does that mean?
[phones chime]
[NAOYA]
No. So many already?
That's gotta be
some kind of mistake, right?
What does this mean?
What rules did they break?
[phones chime]
Dammit, somebody else?
[NOBUAKI]
But why?
Does this mean
that all of them
did something "unnecessary"?
What the hell
is this monster doing?
Naoya! I'm going to call Chiemi
and make sure she's fine.
See if you can talk to anybody
who got a punishment text.
But, why?
I don't know, but it's all
I can think of right now! Hurry!
[line trilling]
Hi! It's Chiemi!
Sorry I can't answer the phone
but leave a message and I'll get
back to you as soon as I can!
Dammit, why aren't you
answering your phone?
Okay, we've gotta
call everybody.
-[line trilling]
-What did he do to break a rule?
-C'mon, answer.
-[line clicks]
Shouta, are you there?
I can't breathe.
Shouta?
His punishment's
already started?
I blocked the bastard.
Don't do it.
He's killing me.
Blocked him?
That's how you broke the rules?
[gasping]
[NOBUAKI]
Shouta? Shouta!
Oh no. Is he dead?
This can't be happening.
How could he be alive
one minute and dead the next?
I have no idea what I'm supposed
to even do right now.
Hey.
What'd he say?
Did he tell you
how he broke the rules?
Is it because he blocked
the messages from the King?
How did you know he did that?
Oh, well, yesterday I overheard
him, Takayuki and Yuusuke.
They were wondering
what would happen
if they blocked the King
and didn't get
any more of the texts.
Those idiots!
Like it could possibly
be that easy
to escape this nightmare.
Didn't they read--
I think I figured it out.
Huh? From the very first texts.
One of the rules was that
you can't drop out of
the game partway through.
Since Shouta, Takayuki,
and Akemi blocked the texts,
they all broke the rules.
That's why they were punished.
I don't think that's
the case with Akemi.
I just called her
and got a message
saying that her number
wasn't in service anymore.
I bet she must have canceled
her entire contract.
So even if you don't have
a phone, the King can kill.
-No way.
-[phone chimes]
But-- No, I didn't do anything!
Please, don't!
Why is this happening to me?
[screams]
[phone ringing]
Oh no! He's not answering
his phone, either!
-[line trilling]
-[NOBUAKI] Chiemi.
Please, you gotta pick up.
She's not answering.
That's it.
I'm gonna go over to her house
and make sure that she's okay.
Yeah. That's a good idea.
Start calling everyone.
No one else can block the King.
And we have to make sure
no one cancels their service.
Right. I'm on it.
You can't do it,
you understand, Hiroko?
Yeah. I got it.
I won't block the King.
[HIROKO] And just try to do
as little as possible.
Sure. I'll just stay
in my room. Thank you.
Okay.
Who else is left?
[phone chimes]
Wait. What?
No way. I just talked to her.
She said she wasn't
gonna do anything!
[phone ringing]
[HIROKO]
It's not fair!
Why is he saying
that I need to be punished?
I swear I didn't do anything.
[NOBUAKI] Are you sure?
Even something small?
I'm telling the truth,
I barely moved at all!
I didn't even have time
to think about anything.
[HIROKO]
Please, I don't want to die!
[crying]
No!
[Hiroko gasps]
[NOBUAKI]
Hiroko? Hiroko! Are you okay?
Say something! Hello?
Please. Say anything.
[phone chimes]
[NOBUAKI]
This is hell.
[NOBUAKI] Hello? Hirofumi?
Are you there?
What's going on?
Please, why me?
I've just been sitting here,
why should I be punished?
I think that we're not
allowed to cry.
I'm sorry.
I realized it too late.
Why are you apologizing?
You didn't do anything.
I'm just a crybaby.
Been that way since I was a kid.
-Hirofumi.
-Bye, Nobuaki.
Thanks for everything
you did for me.
-So long.
-Wait. Don't go!
Hirofumi!
Don't cry. Idiot.
Don't cry.
Don't think about
what's happening.
I can look at it later.
But first I need
to tell everyone
the King thinks crying
is "unnecessary."
[phone ringing]
Hey, what's going on out there?
We need to call everyone again.
Tell them not to read their
texts or talk to anyone today.
-It's too painful.
-But that's nothing new.
[NOBUAKI]
I figured out today's order.
You can't cry.
-If you do, you'll get punished.
-Huh?
If somebody you really
cared about died,
you'd cry, wouldn't you?
In this case
that's a death sentence.
At this rate, none of us
are going to survive.
Okay. So we need to make sure
no one sees who the victims are.
[NAOYA] Got it. I'll start
calling people right now.
Thank you.
[line trilling]
Hi, it's Chiemi!
Sorry I can't--
[line clicks]
This might be the end.
I wish I could have seen Chiemi,
just one last time.
But I've hit my limit.
-I'm sorry. I give up.
-[phone ringing]
Yousuke?
Hey, are you okay?
[NOBUAKI]
Not really.
I don't think I can go through
any more of this.
Pull yourself together, Nobuaki.
It's too soon for you
to be losing hope.
I finally found it.
A major clue
that could end the game.
This could be our best chance.
No way! What is it?
This isn't
the first King's Game,
it's happened before...
in a place
that's not on any maps:
Yonaki Village.
[NOBUAKI]
Yonaki Village?
Yeah, looks like it took place
over thirty years ago.
I'm about to send you
all the info I've got.
You need to go there
and check it out.
Maybe you can figure out
who's doing this.
I'm sorry, Yousuke.
I just don't think
I'm gonna be able to do that.
But I have faith in you.
You can work with Naoya.
The two of you can
take down the King.
[YOUSUKE]
That's not gonna happen.
It's over for me.
This is the last time
you'll hear my voice.
Yousuke? Don't tell me that...
you cried?
[YOUSUKE]
I see now.
So that's what the order meant.
The whole "unnecessary" part.
That's clever.
How could anyone
not cry in this game?
No. Yousuke.
If I end up not
making it through this,
will you take care of her?
For me?
You've got to call Kaori now
before it's too late!
It could be your last chance
to tell her how
you feel about her.
Right now, I only care about you
getting to Yonaki Village.
You have to stop this game.
I can die happy as long
as I know you'll save everyone.
[NOBUAKI] No, maybe I was wrong,
maybe you won't die.
[YOUSUKE]
It's fine.
Just don't let anyone
make Kaori cry.
Keep her safe.
I promise.
I'll take care of her.
Thanks, and goodbye.
Okay. This info should be
all he needs to get there.
[screams]
Not yet.
You won't stop me.
There's no way
I'm gonna die...
before I get this
research to him.
Finish this for me, please.
[panting]
-Now the end.
-[phone ringing]
Kaori?
I want to hear her voice
one more time.
[screams]
Kaori.
[phone continues ringing]
You can't cry.
No matter what,
not a single tear.
Yousuke knew he was gonna die,
but he held it together.
I can, too.
He trusted me to end this.
He did all the research for us.
I won't let his death
be for nothing.
He was right,
it's too soon to lose hope.
It hurts like hell right now,
but I'm gonna fight this
King, dammit.
That's right.
I'm coming for you, bastard.
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
-It's Nobuaki.
Oh.
What's up?
[NOBUAKI]
It's about the King's Game.
Oh, yeah,
Naoya called
and told me not to
block the King
or cancel my service
or anything like that.
[NOBUAKI]
Yeah. Good.
There's one more thing
to add, though.
Mm-hmm?
[NOBUAKI] Whatever happens
today, you can't cry.
-Like, at all.
-Don't cry?
That's what
the order meant earlier.
So you shouldn't look
at your texts,
or talk to anybody
on the phone for that matter.
[KAORI]
All right. Got it. I won't.
Promise me, will you?
Okay. Listen,
did you tell Yousuke?
I've been calling him,
but he's not answering
his phone and I'm kinda worried
'cause I don't think
he'd ignore me.
[NOBUAKI]
It's okay. He's fine.
Oh, really?
I just talked to him,
as a matter of fact.
He said we could
expose the King,
we just have to go
to Yonaki village.
I'm heading there now,
as fast as I can.
You're what? You're not doing
anything crazy, right?
-Remember, you can't cry, okay?
-[line clicks]
Hmm.
I said I was going
to Yonaki Village,
and yet, here I am.
[sighs]
Huh?
Oh! Ow!
Someone hit me.
Where am I?
Wait, was it the King?
Is he here?
Am I gonna be killed?
Help! Someone!
Please, help me!
Anyone?
-[footsteps approaching]
-Oh.
I bet everyone cried for help
just like you are now.
Shouting that
they didn't want to die.
But you still killed them.
You're a murderer!
And now my Yousuke is dead!
You told me he was fine,
that I didn't need to worry.
I liked him
for the longest time,
but I never got a chance
to tell him how I feel.
We were gonna survive
this together.
And after,
I was gonna ask him
if he felt the same way
and wanted to go out with me.
But you lied to me,
and now he's dead.
Tell the truth!
You're the one behind this,
aren't you?
You're wrong!
I promised Yousuke
that I'd end the King's Game
before anyone else got hurt.
-Liar!
-I'm telling the truth!
We talked right before he died.
He sent me the info
he'd gathered on the King.
He trusted me,
so I have to follow through
and go there, now.
Yousuke...
gave everything for us.
I'm sure he wanted
to talk to you.
This damn game.
If it's taught us
anything at all,
it's that life isn't fair!
Listen to me.
Yousuke felt the exact
same way about you!
That's why he asked me
to look after you
if anything were
to happen to him.
He wanted me to make sure
that no matter what,
you didn't have to cry.
[crying]
I'm not gonna let you get away
with making Kaori cry!
What are you doing?
Oh, no. Yousuke.
I won't let his hard work
and sacrifice go to waste.
I promise you.
[footsteps approaching]
Wait, so you're
just gonna let me go?
[phone chimes]
Is that a new text
from the King?
Kaori, you gotta show me
my phone, right now.
Kaori?
[KAORI]
I'm sorry, Nobuaki.
I'll see Yousuke again.
Thank you for telling me
how he felt.
You're crying. Oh, God.
I did it.
This is all my fault.
Please forgive me.
Please, Kaori.
Yousuke.
[footsteps approaching]