Oh, crap. Time's almost up.
We've got 60 seconds!
We're almost there!
Go, go!
So close,
but this game won't end
till the only one left is me.
You're in our way!
[NATSUKO]
This ends here.
[NOBUAKI] I don't have the time
to deal with you, Natsuko.
[screams]
-Are you okay?
-Nobuaki!
Don't wait!
Keep going! Hurry!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[giggling]
After this, I'm gonna get
strong, like they are.
Teru and Nobuaki
will be proud of me.
What? You're running just so
other people will be impressed?
You gotta be strong now.
Don't wait for later, you idiot.
And do it for yourself,
not for anyone else.
Right.
[RYOU]
This is it.
[phone chimes]
A message from the King.
I kind of can't believe
we made it.
Nobuaki. We have to help him.
[NOBUAKI]
No need for that.
I'm right here.
RIONA:
Oh, thank God.
What about the rest?
They should've gotten
here way before us.
You know, I'm pretty sure
you can put Aya down now.
Unless you plan on carrying her
for the rest of the night.
Oh, right.
Ryou.
Will you check to see
how many messages
we got from the King confirming
who made it to the summit?
Yeah, sure, let's see.
Only five.
The four of us and Natsuko.
So, no others made it.
-[chimes]
-Huh?
[gasping]
Look. It's them.
I don't get it. They were all
so far ahead of us.
Something bad must've happened
to them along the way.
[footsteps approach]
Are you behind this,
too, Natsuko?
Tell me!
Aren't you getting
a little tired of blaming me
for other people's mistakes yet?
[spits]
By the way,
not a bad kick,
I can still feel it.
Did you see Takuya and the girls
anywhere on the trails?
Oh, yes.
Our paths crossed.
Unfortunately, all three of them
seemed very disoriented.
I wouldn't be surprised
if they got lost.
It's easy to get hurt out here.
[groans]
[NATSUKO] Losers.
And they were so close.
Now, then,
I wonder what
our next order will be.
Maybe it'll be the final one.
The end.
Who do you think'll win?
-No one wins, you monster.
-[thuds]
[grunts]
[RIONA]
Nobuaki!
Ryou, have you lost
your damn mind?
[rock thuds]
I'm going to get stronger.
I can protect other people,
just like they always tried to.
[RIONA]
What are you talking about?
We got a new order.
We have to make a human doll.
To do that, we have to cut
our own bodies into pieces
and put them together.
We need a head, torso,
two arms, and two legs.
They can all be from the same
person or some from each of us.
The thing is,
we have to cut ourselves.
No. There's no way
we can do that.
We've had some pretty sick
commands in the last few days,
but this is beyond disgusting.
We're just high school students.
We're real people!
Not just body parts
to play with!
What, are we supposed
to glue the parts together?
He's treating us like we're
a bunch of serial killers.
No need to worry.
I'll cut off all my limbs
so you guys don't have to.
I'll die. The only problem is,
I can't cut off my own head.
You think that's the problem?
Are you even listening
to how crazy you sound?
You said you wanted
to become stronger.
But this is suicide!
No. I'm sacrificing myself
for my friends.
[gasps]
Here you go. Now, my advice
would be to do it fast
before the shock wears off.
This is perfect, seriously.
This entire time, I've been
wanting to help everyone else.
Just like Teru helped Nobuaki.
-Ryou, no!
-I can protect all of you.
[saw rumbling]
[rumbling stops]
-Put it down.
-Stay back!
Someone has to be dismembered.
We both know that.
[RYOU gasps]
[NATSUKO]
Okay, Ryou.
Pull the starter again, hard.
And this time,
hold down the button. Got it?
I'm going to become a real man!
-[saw buzzing]
-No matter what it takes!
[screaming]
Yeah, that's the way, Ryou!
-Keep going!
-Stop him, please!
Oh, no, looks like
it's stuck on your bone.
No problem.
[screaming]
I'm here to help
a friend in need.
[screaming]
-[leg thuds]
-[RYOU whimpers]
[NATSUKO] That's one, Ryou.
But you've got three more to go.
If you're not careful, you'll
bleed out before you finish up.
Oh, dear.
You're already dead?
♪
[RIONA sobs]
I can't.
This is too horrible.
[saw rumbling]
-[gasps]
-So, what should we do next?
Would it be rude to wake Aya
and Nobuaki with this chain saw?
You... you aren't even human.
You're some kind of demon!
I won't let you hurt any of us.
[scoffs] Look at you,
cowering on the ground.
What do you think
you're going to do?
[MATSUOKA] You killed Ryou,
didn't you? Didn't you?
You'll pay for this!
Bring him back!
Ryou was too good to die!
Shut up.
And stay outta my way!
[chain saw buzzing]
Well, that's great.
Looks like Aya's
down for the count
and we'll have to do
the work for her.
-No. Don't.
-Where should we cut first?
Stop this. Please, someone help.
I can't take it.
[scoffs]
You always acted like you were
so high and mighty in class.
"Someone help me!"
"I can't take it!"
It's adorable.
"Helpless" is
a good look for you.
There's only one problem.
No one's going
to save you, Riona.
[chain saw revving]
[NOBUAKI]
Stop it!
[RIONA]
Nobuaki!
-Why'd you do this to Ryou?
-It's our new order.
We're supposed to cut our bodies
to pieces and make a doll.
Catch up, please.
The kid actually
did it to himself.
Ryou did this before we could
even talk about it?
[RIONA]
He wanted to.
He said he was going to become
stronger, like Teruaki.
He wanted to be more like you.
[NOBUAKI] But you already
were strong, Ryou.
You were so small,
but you ran all this way,
up a whole mountain.
You were exhausted,
but you kept encouraging
everyone to keep going.
You're far more of a man
than I am.
You were scared, weren't you?
I know.
But you hung in there.
Well, what happens now?
Do we dig graves
or just continue?
We're supposed to cut up
our own bodies?
Why would he give us
such a sick order?
What does it matter to him
if we make a human doll?
Who cares why he wants us
to do anything?
All that matters is
we're going to do it.
[NOBUAKI] We can't keep
following these insane demands!
There's barely any of us
left as it is.
Okay, you have to help me think.
Come on. There has to be
some way to survive this.
All of us. Isn't there anything
we can do to stop him?
What don't you get?
There's no stopping him,
so suck it up!
Wait.
Before you got here, you were
plotting something together.
What were you and Riona
talking about?
What are you planning?
Nobuaki,
maybe we should
work together with her.
She might know something.
We have a few clues
as to how the game works.
Everyone who dies gets
a one-syllable text
sent to their phone.
We collected these.
So, do you have any idea
what they could mean?
How 'bout that.
I'm actually impressed.
I didn't think you idiots
had noticed anything.
I caught on to the same thing
when I played the game
at my last high school.
I've been collecting them
since the first order this time.
So far, I haven't been able
to spell out anything
that makes sense.
Hey, maybe if we put the letters
we collected together with hers,
they'll form
some kind of sentence.
Yeah.
It's like just Ria was saying.
The King's Game is
basically a type of virus
that originated in Yonaki
Village a long time ago.
Yonaki Village.
[NOBUAKI] At some point,
it moved onto the Internet.
Now it exists online.
It's like some kind of mutated
computer virus or something.
That's what's to blame
for these orders.
Let's put our heads together.
If we're lucky, we'll finally
figure out how to beat the game.
Well, this Ria girl's theories
sound ridiculous.
I'm not sure I believe
any of that nonsense.
If you think we're stupid,
then why have you been
collecting all these texts too?
They're the only lead we've got.
The only clue we have
to unlocking the secrets
of this damn game.
You must think so too.
Otherwise you wouldn't have gone
out of your way to find them.
I didn't do it to end the game
or try to save anybody
or to beat the King,
whatever the hell that means.
I just wanted as much
information as possible
that might help me survive.
Plain and simple. That's it.
You're serious.
[NATSUKO]
Give me that.
-Look.
-Oh, crap.
That has to be it.
That means...
This can't be right. No way.
So basically, none of us
can keep on living
if we really want
to end the game.
The King's Game virus
lives in the bodies
of everyone
who's had to play before.
It keeps on spreading
through whoever won.
If you survive, it could pass
from you to others,
and the game will continue
until humanity is wiped out.
Every person on Earth,
killed by a single plague.
In order for us
to end this game,
not a single participant
can live when it's over.
If we want to save
every person in the world,
we're all going to have
to die tonight.
It's not fair, at all.
We used to be ordinary kids:
going to school, getting excited
over sports and new students.
Everything was normal.
And now the world
is in our hands?
It's insanity.
[NATSUKO laughing]
So what if everyone dies?
There's only one person
I care about.
I bet you're thinking about
trying to be some kind of savior
by sacrificing yourself
to save all of mankind.
Always thinking
you can fix everything.
I'm so tired of it.
If we're all going
to die anyway,
I'll do you a favor
and kill you myself!
What are you doing?
I'm going to survive this.
I'm not gonna give up yet.
Both of us survived our games,
but that's obviously the only
thing we have in common.
Weren't you changed by all the
horrors you had to go through?
Didn't you feel anything
watching your friends
die terrible,
painful deaths after suffering
at the hands of this bastard?
Didn't you learn anything
when the person you loved died?
It made me realize
what my duty really was.
To quickly end the pain
and suffering the others
were going through.
Someone has to be the bad guy
in the King's Game.
Someone has to push everyone
to the extreme. You see?
That's the part I played.
You're delusional.
But you, I can't forgive you
for filling them
with your false hope,
saying everything
would be okay in the end.
I don't care
if everyone else hates me.
At least I'm not
a liar like you.
That's even worse!
-[chain saw buzzing]
-[screaming]
[RIONA]
I won't let you kill Nobuaki!
He means too much to me.
He got us this far!
[chain saw stops]
[gasps, groans]
Was I wrong to try
and give everyone hope?
No, you can't listen to her.
I don't know.
She made sense.
Nobuaki,
I want you to look at me.
-I'm looking.
-I'm here only because of you.
You're why I'm alive now.
You did the right thing.
Otherwise, I'd be dead
on the side of the road.
You know, I'd do it again
in a heartbeat.
[RIONA]
Hey, before all this happened,
how long did you think
you'd live?
It doesn't have to be that long.
Why?
Because all I want is
to be able to spend
a little of that time with you.
I love you!
I just wish I'd known sooner!
-[chain saw buzzing]
-Aah!
You're coming with me.
[RIONA]
No!
If you love a person,
it's better to end their life
with your own two hands...
♪
...than to let
someone else do it.
I won't give him to you.
He's mine.
♪
-Natsuko...
-It's okay, my Nobu.
-Nobuaki!
-Riona...
Just focus on me,
and I can stop the bleeding.
It's over.
She cut me way too deep.
No. Don't say that.
There has to be a way!
[RIONA sobbing]
[NOBUAKI]
Make me a promise.
Survive this.
Will you do that
one thing for me?
But I can't.
I'm not strong enough
to keep going.
So you're not allowed
to die yet.
You hear me?
Don't go, Nobuaki. Nobuaki?
No.
[sobs]
Nobuaki!
♪
Nobuaki, there you are.
Chiemi, it's you!
You're all here.
♪
I know this seems weird.
But it is kind of romantic,
us alone on the beach?
Sorry for dragging you
all the way out here.
You're freezing.
I warmed you up
this way last time.
Come on.
At least open your eyes.
I'm ordering you to kiss me.
[RIONA sobbing]
You can't just lay there
and ignore me.
I'm begging you to wake up!
♪
-[GIRL 1] Good morning!
-[GIRL 2] Hi!
[students chattering]
[chiming]
What the hell?
A game?