Just who I wanted to talk to.
You have a lot
of explaining to do.
Oh? Tell me, are you still
with Kenta and Mizuki?
I bet they look so cute.
They're cuddled up next
to each other, aren't they?
-What did you do? Tell me now!
-[NATSUKO] This is a relief.
I was waiting all day
to get a text from her
telling me to die.
Let me guess.
Kenta sent it instead.
Basically, as soon as that text
came in, I screwed Teruaki.
That way, an "obedience
confirmed" message
got sent out to everyone.
[giggles]
I figured Kenta
would totally misunderstand
and think it was for Mizuki.
So, I was right.
That guy was an idiot.
I'm surprised
he survived this long.
She was doomed the second
she switched devices,
but he still tried
to save her
How sweet.
It's perfect.
This way Kenta got exactly
what he wanted from the start.
He died with his timid
little girlfriend
-blushing at his side.
-Shut up!
[NATSUKO]
Ooh, are sure that you want
to talk to me like that?
Why shouldn't I?
You do remember
it's your phone
I'm calling from, right?
Well, enjoy your night.
See you soon, Nobu.
-Buh-bye.
-No, wait! Hello?
Poor little Nobu,
your life is in my hands.
And I'm going to make sure
that you die next.
[breathing shakily]
Crap.
Natsuko's friggin' crazy.
She's out to kill Nobuaki
and after that, she'll probably
come for the rest of us.
I've gotta figure out
a way to stop her.
Teruaki.
-[pounding on door]
-What are you doing in there?
Answer me.
I hope
you're not plotting anything.
No way! I'd never do that.
[pounding continues]
Stop it!
Just leave me alone!
[pounding stops]
[NATSUKO]
My dear Teruaki.
[screams]
You know you can't betray me.
Because if you do,
I'll kill you.
Understand?
[NOBUAKI "So far, I haven't been
able to verify many things
"regarding the origins
of the King's Game.
"But there is one fact
I can confirm
"with absolute certainty.
"Everyone who died
as a victim in the King's Game
"received a single letter
or syllable
"around the time of their death.
"It's odd.
This is a new phenomenon.
Something that didn't happen
in the game I was a part of."
Those letters.
Just like Ria said.
[RIA]
I think these were likely caused
by some kind of bug
in the King's Game program.
Maybe they're something
I can exploit.
[NOBUAKI] "I don't know
what these letters mean
"or their significance.
"Some people believe that they
are the result of a mutation
"within the game itself,
an unexpected by-product
"that even the King
did not anticipate.
"In this game
that is so full of absolutes,
"I believe this mutation
will be the key
"to ending the King
and his terrors
once and for all."
Mutation.
So, it was a bug.
Ria's theory was correct
in some ways.
Kenta got sent one
of these messages, too.
Which means I should be
collecting all the symbols.
-[phone ringing]
-Uh...
I wonder why
she'd be calling Kenta.
-Uh, hello?
-[RIONA] Nobuaki? Huh.
So you really were
with the two of them.
-Riona?
-Good, you can read.
But don't talk to me
like you know me.
You and I aren't friends.
Can you try to remember that?
Yeah, sure.
What's going on?
Why were you trying
to call Kenta?
[RIONA] Yeah, we should cut
to the chase.
But I'm not gonna share
my intel over the phone.
[NOBUAKI]
Intel? What does that mean?
Did you hear me?
I'll tell you, but you have
to come to my house immediately.
[NOBUAKI]
Sorry, no can do.
I'm actually
a good ways outside of town.
It'll take me a while
to get back.
Maybe around noon?
Yeah, fine,
I guess that'll work.
But you'd better
come straight here.
-Uh, hello, excuse me?
-[RIONA] Yes?
Hey, it's me Kanazawa.
-It took me a while to--
-[RIONA] Finally!
I have been waiting for you.
You're late.
Yeah, I know.
But the trains were
a little behind schedule.
I don't wanna hear excuses.
Am I gonna have
a problem with you?
Um, I don't think so?
Come on. We're going.
Uh, I thought you had
something to tell me.
-At least try to keep up.
-With what?
I don't want my parents
to see you.
What if they thought I was
sneaking you into my room?
Now follow me.
Yeah. Sure.
[BOYS laughing]
[NOBUAKI]
This is where we're going?
Is that a problem?
[NOBUAKI] I guess not.
So, what's on your mind?
The only thing that could be.
The game obviously.
You're not the only one who's
been trying to investigate it.
You likely haven't
seen this yet.
But look.
We're not alone.
Something similar
to our game happened
at another school
not too long ago.
I found several articles
about it.
That's not all.
There's a familiar name
in these reports.
Her. Our "darling" Natsuko.
So, it's true.
[RIONA] She was hiding
all of this from us.
She knew about the King's Game.
I think she survived it.
Yeah.
[RIONA] You don't seem
surprised by any of this.
Okay. What about her?
Iwamura Ria.
Uh!
Wait, how do you know that name?
Oh. So then, you do know her.
How? Answer me now.
Get your filthy hands off me.
Sorry.
But... how do you know
about Ria?
She wasn't difficult to find.
I assure you that my research
was very thorough.
Eventually,
it led me to your old school
where you'd played before.
That's when I found something.
Read this.
Start talking, Nobuaki.
Who is Ria?
What do these words mean?
How is this all connected
to the King's Game?
Ria was one of my classmates.
She was consumed by flames
after breaking one
of the King's rules.
And, as far as those
words and stuff go,
she was collecting
the one-syllable texts
that everyone who died
in the game receives.
Look.
There's more here.
According to what
I've been reading,
there was a King's Game
before the ones Natsuko
and I were part of.
This notebook was left behind
by a person who played it.
It also mentions
the short messages.
It's so strange.
But this can't just be
a coincidence.
They could be the key
that frees us.
Interesting.
I was thinking the same thing.
Here are the ones
that I collected.
I saw Natsuko messing around
with Yuuichi's phone
at the park
right after he died.
I thought she might
have found a clue,
so I checked it out later.
-Good thinking!
-Yeah. I know.
Anyway, I noticed something else
once I started digging further.
What am I supposed
to be seeing here?
Wait. Are you saying
these syllables are the same?
-I think they are.
-Okay, that's good.
Between the ones I have now
and the ones
I collected last time...
We might end up
solving this.
Yeah.
We might!
Thank goodness.
Hey. Whoa.
Nobuaki, are you okay?
[NOBUAKI] All that death
wasn't for nothing.
My friends. Everyone.
Their lives mattered in the end.
I'll stop him.
[crying]
Thank you.
You've given me
a little bit of hope again.
[NATSUKO]
My, my, my.
You look like you're having
a good time, Nobu.
[NOBUAKI]
Natsuko!
What were you two
talking about, huh?
[RIONA] Why are you
all the way out here?
I came to track down
the two of you.
Everyone else is waiting
at Shibafu Field.
[NOBUAKI]
Before we go anywhere...
I need answers.
About what?
Can we talk in private?
Fine.
Private enough for you?
Should I be worried
you'll take advantage of me?
Natsuko.
You had to play the King's Game
before just like me, didn't you?
What does that matter?
Did you get an order
saying you had
to murder someone yourself?
Did you have to kill?
Of course I did.
And I didn't hesitate.
And was there
someone special to you?
One of the other players,
I mean.
There was.
Is that who you killed?
Bingo. I killed them.
It's the only reason
I'm still alive.
Damn it.
Why're you bringing this up?
None of it has anything
to do with you.
I think it does.
Natsuko...
when you were little,
did you have a sister?
One who you were separated from.
A girl named Honda Chiemi?
-[NATSUKO] How do you?
-She's my special person.
Oh, really?
Is that how it is?
Natsuko. Listen. I think we--
Idiot.
[chuckles]
Let me guess.
You thought we could come
to some sort of understanding
just because I'm related
to your dead girlfriend.
You are such
an unbelievably naive child.
But that's what I dig
about you, Nobu, babe.
Love ya.
[NOBUAKI]
What's wrong with you.
If that's all, then let's go.
We'll be late.
Wait a sec.
Why're you getting us together?
What terrible thing
are you planning?
[NATSUKO]
Oh, didn't I tell you?
I'm going to carry out
the next order.
It's been fun.
But you're dead next.
[RYOU] Teruaki.
Do you really mean that?
I do. Help me.
[leaves rustling]
[NATSUKO] Sorry for keeping
everyone waiting.
Teruaki. It's good to see you.
I'm so glad you're safe.
-Nobuaki, listen to me.
-Sure, what's up?
No. Don't worry about it.
Good. It looks like
we're all here.
Shall we begin the next game?
There's no point in waiting.
[TERUAKI] Okay. Everyone's seen
the new order, right?
[NOBUAKI]
Oh, no. I'm still in the dark.
Of course you are.
Here.
Give me a sec.
So, we're supposed
to do this one at a time
in the order
of our seat numbers.
Each player can cut off
any number of fingers
during their turn.
Or just breaking them
will work, too.
Each destroyed finger
has a point value
that must be assigned
to someone in the class.
Fingers on the right hand
are worth one positive point.
Fingers on the left hand,
one negative point.
We can spread the points across
multiple people if we want to.
Whoever ends the game
with a negative score
will be punished.
Oh, man.
So basically,
if someone breaks the fingers
on their left hand,
they can give you
negative points.
But then you could just mangle
the fingers on your right hand
to get yourself out of danger.
This can't be happening.
I'm cringing just thinking about
how much it's gonna hurt.
There's no reason for you
to freak everyone out like that.
What do you mean?
The King says you can
give points to yourself.
But he also says you can pass
when it's your turn, no problem.
Ugh!
[NOBUAKI] Including me,
there are eleven survivors here.
This is how they'd be arranged
by their seat numbers.
The problem is that the last
person to go will be Aimi,
Natsuko's best friend.
If she breaks even one finger
and assigns it to someone else,
they're dead.
They'd have no chance
to save themselves.
Natsuko, can I say
something before we start?
-Have an idea?
-What is it?
I have something of a proposal.
Isn't it time for us
to stop fighting?
-So I'm the bad guy now?
-No!
But we should be thinking of
a way for all of us to survive
instead of trying to get this
over with as fast as we can.
-Go to hell.
-What's your problem?
The best thing for you to do
right now is follow my orders.
So you're just as bad
as the King.
That's enough out of you.
Do you understand what will
happen if you disobey me?
-Is that your phone?
-Yeah. Afraid so.
-She stole it from me earlier.
-Of course.
I'm done talking.
-Let's get started.
-It'll be okay.
-You sure?
-Oh, yeah.
A bunch of us agree
with Teruaki.
We never forgot
what you said to us before.
At the park.
When this was first starting.
If you guys don't want to die,
if you don't wanna see
your friends murdered,
we have to work together.
I was so confused,
but I think I understand now.
We should be looking
for a way to save
our remaining classmates
from getting hurt.
Ryou.
[NOBUAKI]
Wait. This is simple.
For this order,
as long as everyone passes,
no one will be punished.
But is that really plausible?
Do we have that much faith
in each other?
[MASATOSHI]
I'm first. I pass.
You're next, Kanazawa.
What you gonna do?
Wait, not so fast.
What's your deal?
Are you really sure that
passing's the smartest idea?
I made my choice.
And they're right.
This is no time for us
to be fighting with each other.
Damn it.
If even one person breaks
a finger on their left hand,
this falls apart.
[RYOU]
Hey, Nobu.
Please pass.
It'll be best for all of us.
Yeah. But what if...
You have to put
your trust in us.
Does that mean...
I'm also passing.
You're too soft.
You won't win this.
Thank you. Nobuaki.
Watch to the end,
no matter what happens, okay.
Things could get intense.
Okay.
I'm gonna pass as well.
Yeah, same here.
There's no reason
any innocent people
need to get hurt playing this.
[NATSUKO]
What in the hell's going on?
This can't all be because
of Teruaki's little outburst.
[NOBUAKI]
It's so peaceful today,
even though we're playing
this monstrous game.
I thought this was going to end
up being a brutal struggle,
but it's almost nice.
Yeah, I'm gonna pass, too.
[NOBUAKI]
Only six people left to go.
Teruaki Riona, Natsuko
and then Aya, Rina, and Aimi.
That means I'm the next one up.
Nobuaki, can I borrow you
for a second first?
Uh, yeah, sure.
[NATSUKO]
Are you kidding me?
This won't take long.
So, what's this haircut
all about?
You've let yourself
get pretty shaggy.
No way you'll get a girlfriend
with all this hiding your face.
-Probably not.
-Hurry it up.
We're in the middle
of a game, remember?
I know. That's why I'm here.
When everything looks like
it's going to hell,
you should do
what you can to help out.
Don't you think?
[scoffs]
Just get it over with fast.
That girl is just the worst.
What's really going on?
I feel like there's something
in front of me that I'm missing.
You'll find out.
Do you think
he's really going to be able
to go through with this plan?
I don't know.
But, honestly, I really hope
he ends up
chickening out before he can.
[NOBUAKI]
You're pretty good at this.
[chuckles]
Thanks a lot.
I want to be
a hair stylist one day
That's awesome.
I forgot you offered
to cut my hair for me
when I moved here.
It's good practice.
I guess you could
call this my dream.
After I graduate high school,
my plan is to go
to a cosmetology program.
Just you wait. I'm going to be
a celebrity hairdresser.
Wow, you sure are confident.
[chuckles]
My 45,000 yen shears help too.
-Holy crap.
-[laughing]
And these aren't
even top of the line.
I guess I don't really know that
much about the world of hair.
Here we go.
[NATSUKO] All right, wrap it up,
would ya? I'm bored.
This joke has dragged
on long enough.
You almost done?
Don't worry,
it'll all be over real soon.
Just gotta trust me.
[NOBUAKI] I didn't know Teruaki
had such a big heart.
I really hope his dreams
come true one day.
I want him to live.
I want him to have a future.
There. All done.
-Thanks, man.
-You like it?
-It's much better.
-I'm so glad.
One last cut while I can.
[screams]
No, what are you doing?
Wait! What's going on?
Why didn't he pass?
Teruaki! No more!
Do you really like
your hair?
Be honest with me.
What do you think?
[grunts]
It's great. S-Seriously.
The best cut I've ever had!
Thank you so much.
So you can stop.
Got it?
If you keep going, you won't
ever hold scissors again!
[TERUAKI]
Keep your cool, Nobuaki.
Broken bones will heal
over the course of time.
I'm just playing up
the pain for our audience.
What? Tell me your plan!
I'm getting our phones back
from Natsuko
before she breaks them.
And I got everyone else
in on it, too.
Then that means
you're the reason
everyone else has passed.
I'm not gonna
let her murder us.
No way!
But what are you
gonna do next?
I'm going to teach her a lesson.
I won't take any more threats.
I'm gonna prove to her that
we're stronger together.
To do that...
I need to have lots
of negative points.
No! Stop!
I'll give my entire
left hand to the King.
Natsuko! What are
you gonna do now?
Teruaki!