Hey everyone,
Kaleido Star's about to start,
so make sure that
your room is brightly lit,
and that you're not sitting
too close to the TV!
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
Everyone expects me to be the
energetic girl that
I was before!
But that's hard because too many
sad things have happened;
I almost gave up on my dream,
and I made my friends worry.
Nobody wants to see
me cry... do they?
No, they want me to smile!
Oh yeah, smiles!
Not just mine, but everybody's!
My dream is a Kaleido Stage with
no competition and
lots of smiles.
I can do it, I can, I can!
What's wrong with you?
Why won't you even try?
Why do you keep running
away from competition?
You coward!
I think you should take some
time and think how your
refusal to compete just
now has affected May.
Sometimes you can hurt someone
just as much by not fighting.
Maybe what Miss Layla said is
true, maybe I did hurt May.
But even if I did,
I still don't want to
compete on stage ever again.
My dream is to recreate
the fun Kaleido Stage
that I saw when I
was a little girl.
And I won't ever give
up on my dream again.
Someday, if everyone works
together, we can make it happen!
If only I could get
May and Leon to agree.
Leon?
Sophie...I'm so happy.
Leon's eyes have
never looked so kind.
I wonder...who is Sophie?
"An Amazingly
Humiliating Performance."
Sophie.
Partner?
Nobody can be Leon's partner.
Nobody but her.
Sophie must be the
one she was talking about.
So this Sophie person
is the only one
who could be Leon's partner.
But...why did Leon
call Sora by that name?
So she is the one after all.
Okay everybody, break a leg!
Thanks a lot Sora.
I hate asking you to do this...
No, don't worry
about it, it's my job!
Let me know if
you need anything.
Huh?
The one who can become
my partner is...Sora Naegino.
How are you Leon?
It looks like today I'm
gonna be the one scattering
the flower petals
over you and May.
I'll do my best and scatter
them hard...wait a minute,
that sounds kinda
weird, doesn't it?
Well you know what I mean!
Anyway, I hope that you
have a great show today.
See ya!
I won the World Festival
and Sora withdrew.
Now I'm the top star
and she's just a gofer.
Sora ran away from the chance
to compete yesterday too.
I keep winning all
the battles,
but she's always two
steps ahead of me!
Hey Leon, I wanna
know who Sophie is.
Is it true that
Sophie's the only
one who can become your partner?
I don't doubt that whoever
she is, she's amazing.
But I'm confident that I can be
even more amazing than Sophie!
I'll prove it to you that
I can do anything
that Sophie could
do, only better!
I'm the one who can
become your partner, I know it!
The whole world's acknowledged
my talent, so why can't you!
I'll prove it to you,
I'll beat Sora and Sophie!
You can't.
But why not?!
If you haven't figured that
out yet, you won't even be
able to beat Sora,
let alone Sophie.
You won't even be able to
beat Sora, let alone Sophie.
What's wrong with me?
What does Sora
have that I don't?
What could it be?
Let's adjust the
timetable everybody.
Plus thirty seconds please.
May's even worse than yesterday.
She looks bored.
She does.
How are you today Leon?
It looks like today I'm
gonna be the one scattering
the flower petals
over you and May.
But, what...Leon!
Come on.
Huh?
Please don't do this Leon.
Release the trapeze immediately.
Yes ma'am.
I'm going back up.
Please, just let me
get off stage!
So you've finally made
it back on stage Sora.
Let's settle this today!
Please stop May!
No, wait!
The audience doesn't
know what's going on.
Okay.
I'll have to perform...for them!
Are you ready to
face me now, Sora?
Oh my gosh!
I don't know,
but this is awesome!
You won't even be able to
beat Sora, let alone Sophie.
I want to win.
I've got to win!
I have to beat Sora!
May's turning out a
decent performance.
She's so passionate,
it's like she's trying to
take Romeo's love by force!
I've never seen
a Juliet like this!
And Sora's performance
is so energetic that
May's intensity can't
even touch her.
She's got such presence.
You can tell that she
loves being on stage.
I'm gonna fall!
I can hear it.
I can hear the
audience's applause.
I love it.
That was the...
the "Angel's Maneuver"
she did at the festival.
Leon's so passionate now.
Leon...
He's being so kind to her.
Is he just acting?
Or...did I lose again?
Leon, I...I've got
to get back to work.
So would you please finish the
show with May as your Juliet?
Sophie.
No!
Sophie, wait!
Don't leave me!
Leon!
No, Leon!
I've heard that Leon
will have to spend the
next two or three
weeks in hospital.
Thank goodness
he's a lightweight,
or his injuries could have
been much more severe.
So Kaleido Stage is shut
down for about a month?
I hope that's the worst of it.
I'm just glad that Ken
killed the lights quickly.
I mean it would have
been terrible if the audience
had seen Leon hit the ground.
So the Kids Stage
is shut down too?
I'm afraid so Marion.
That poor audience
saw a performance
that wasn't any fun at all.
It's not your fault Sora.
Even monkeys
can fall outta trees.
Leon was bound
to fall eventually.
Hurry Sora!
It feels so good out here.
Coming!
You're right, it does
feel good doesn't it.
Told ya!
May!
I'm sorry, things kinda
got out of control.
Did you visit Leon
in the hospital?
Why should I visit him?
I mean, I'm not even
really Leon's partner yet.
Do you have any
idea who Sophie is?
Um, no I don't.
Sophie's probably the
only person in the
world who can
become Leon's partner.
And for some reason, Leon
sees you and thinks of Sophie.
You're the one he wants
to perform with, not me.
But...but I don't know why!
He knows that my
contract's been terminated,
and I'm not even
allowed on stage.
I guess you just
remind him of her.
She must have been dense too.
I don't think I've ever met
anyone as dense as you.
You've beaten me again,
even though you refuse
to compete with me.
And you didn't
even realize it, did you?
I beat you?
Umm May, I think you've
got that backwards.
You're so dense!
Super dense!
Totally dense!
Extra special dangerously dense!
Despite that, I'll admit that
even though I don't know
what it is, you've got
something special that I don't.
So I've decided to try my best
to be a little more humble.
I'll be so humble that I'll
finally beat you, and I'll watch
you squirm while I
become a Kaleido Star!
See ya.
Yeah, see ya.
What was so humble about that?
All of the insurance
procedures and the
related issues are
going smoothly.
Good.
Yes, come in?
We've been expecting
you Mr. Kenneth.
The Kaleido Stage
has been shut down?
So tell me, is this part
of your plan, Kalos?
No sir.
Part of your plan?
And who are you, boy?
My name is Ken Robbins, sir.
And Sora, how is she doing?
She's depressed.
For some reason, she feels that
she's partly to blame for Leon.
You can't open the doors again
until this gets worked out.
That's right, sir.
We thought that they
would make a good pair,
but maybe they're
not fit to be partners.
We shouldn't write
them off yet sir.
It's possible that what
happened today could
trigger something
in both of them.
I guess you're right Kalos.
I'll just wait a little longer
and see how things play out.
Only time will tell
if Leon Oswald
has the ability to be
Sora's partner.
They're questioning
Leon and not Sora?
If Sora and Leon can
work out their problems
and become partners,
I believe that
Kaleido Stage will flourish,
and Sora along with it.
You can look forward to it.
What are they trying
to make Sora do?
You know, I wonder if
Miss Layla and Miss Cathy
are planning on going
back to Broadway?
The shows have like all
been cancelled, you know?
But I totally think they wanna
stay at Kaleido Stage forever.
Like, is someone coming?
That Sora's got some talent,
don't you think so Layla?
It just seems like she's growing
into this great performer,
but none of the people
around her seem to notice it.
Well, I may very well
be one of those people.
What do you mean?
I think I might have made
a huge mistake with Sora.
She is this innocent and sincere
girl who loves Kaleido Stage.
She jumped into
all of this alone,
with nothing but
aspirations in her heart.
I entrusted Sora with my dream.
I wanted her
to reach that
faraway place
that I never could.
I thought that no
matter how cruel the
path may be Sora could succeed.
After all, it's the only path I
know to become a Kaleido Star.
But maybe I shouldn't have
expected such ruthlessness
from such a
sweet girl like Sora.
And then on the other side of
the spectrum, you've got May.
I'm just wondering
what you think,
'cuz I think I've
got her figured out.
You do?
Yeah, think about it;
she doesn't have anyone
to look up to,
so she gets frustrated,
and then she takes
it out on Sora and Leon.
She needs someone to
set goals for her and to be
a mentor to help
draw out her talent.
She just doesn't have
anyone to do that for her.
If she truly needs a goal,
then her best bet would be
to think of the potential
that her future holds.
That's always
been my personal goal.
That works for you
but not everyone's
as strong as you are, Layla.
Miss Layla!
You have a guest!
I'm sorry to interrupt you Miss
Layla, but you've got a guest.
Umm, Miss Layla?
I've come here to ask
you a special favor.
I know you've retired from
Kaleido Stage, and I probably
shouldn't be asking
this favor of you, but...
Please Miss Layla,
I want you to train me!
I just...I really want to
figure out what
Sora's got that I don't.
And I really want
to improve my skills.
So please Miss Layla,
will you help me?
I think we should help her.
We've got nothing better to do.
That's true.
I guess I'll do it.
Thank you very much!
It's such a beautiful
day today that I thought
it would be nice to
have our tea outside.
Great idea!
But don't you think we should
invite Mia and Anna to join us?
Well everyone's busy
doing other things since
we've got this sudden vacation.
Oh.
I just wanted to tell you
that you were really
great up on stage yesterday.
Even Mia and the
others were amazed.
To tell you the truth Rosetta,
somewhere along the
way I started having fun.
Yeah, I could tell!
I think that the backstage
job is a lot of fun,
but I also think that the
stage is where I really belong.
Yeah, I think so too!
When I heard the
audience's applause,
it made me so happy... that I
didn't even feel upset anymore.
I felt like the audience was
sending me positive energy.
The move you did yesterday was
the "Angel's Maneuver", right?
Yeah.
Is it hard to do?
Yeah, I guess it is.
So which part's the hardest?
Hmm, the hardest part of the
"Angel's Maneuver"...well,
it's like you're flying
through the air,
WHOOSH, and while you're up
there your partner looks so far
away, but you have to get close,
'cuz you have to grab hands,
then he catches you SHOOM,
then you swing SHOOM, so,
did that make any sense?
Nope, not at all.
That figures.
It sounds like
a really hard stunt.
It is, especially since I don't
know enough of the basics.
I gave Yuri a tough time while
he was teaching it to me.
Hey, then why don't we start
working on our basics together?
No, it's getting late.
Let's take a bath together
and smooch while she stays...
It's still the afternoon!!
You are so mean to me!
Is it bad to do basics in
the afternoon, Sora?
Oh no Rosetta, I was
just talking to myself.
No May.
Try it again.
Okay.
I'm not buying it!
May, at this point we'll
go for any emotion.
Okay.
No good.
Look, your audience is Cathy
right now, do you understand?
Yes ma'am.
Then continue.
Alright.
No good.
Eugh, no no good!
I overslept!
A ticket to the Kids Stage?
Welcome!
Ken, why are you
dressed like that?
And when did you learn
how to ride a unicycle?
Well I originally wanted to be
part of the cast, you know?
But I had to quit because
I got a weak heart.
But that's beside the point.
Now I welcome you
to the special show
that we've created
just for you Sora!
Welcome to the Special Stage!
We realized you've never
had the chance to sit back
and just enjoy a
show since you've
come to join us on
the Kaleido Stage,
Sora.
So we've prepared a special show
for you, our special guest.
I hope you like it.
It was tough
keeping it a secret!
Sit back, relax,
and enjoy this special show
we've prepared for you!
And now, on to the Special
Show for our dear Sora.
Let's go!
Oh wow!
Wow, Rosetta,
Marion, that's awesome!
Ta da!
Jonathan, you're so good!
Oh yeah!
Wow, how cool!
One...and two!
Wow!
That's it Anna, you've got it!
Anna you're a natural!
She's laughing,
it's now or never.
Oh, I tea!
Sorry.
Yay!
I have such incredible friends.
They did this just
to cheer me up!
We love...Sora!
My friends and the audience are
what gives me my strength.
With their support,
I could even become a star.
A real Kaleido Star!
I'm ready to go back on
stage with my friends.
I wanna give
it all I've got,
and perform for the
audiences that I love!
I wanna create a fun show that
we can all enjoy...together.
The Kaleido Stage
should always be fun like this.
I love it!
It seems that Sagittarius was
finally able to regain
its brilliance.
However, a shooting
star is approaching,
and is aspiring for
the same brilliance.
This star...whose
star could this be?
The Perfect Dating Manual: 100
Ways to Captivate Her Heart!
Ken's invited me out to lunch!
Hang in there Ken.
Yeah, show us what
kinda man you are!
It's time to be brave, brave!
That's right, you take the lead
Ken, right Mr. Policeman?
What?
What!
Next time on Kaleido Star: "Mr.
Policeman's Amazing Proposal."
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky.