Kaleido Stage.
It's neither a circus,
nor a musical.
It's not magic, either.
What it is, is the best
entertainment show in the world.
And there was a girl
who aspired to join Kaleido
Stage and become a star.
She is sixteen
year-old Sora Naegino.
However, the theatre
she's dreamed of is being
taken away from her.
Will Sora and her friends
ever get Kaleido Stage back?
Some call me the Fool.
I am the spirit of the stage.
I have only been
seen by a chosen few.
And right now, Sora Naegino
is the only one who can see me.
With her talent
and determination,
she has made steady progress
on the path to becoming a star.
Last time, she even
had the chance to appear
on stage with her idol,
Layla Hamilton.
Just when Kaleido Stage was
showing a surge in popularity,
Sora and her friends began
to experience ordeals they
had never encountered before.
The betrayer- Yuri Killiam.
The current production
will be dismantled after
this evening's performance.
You're going to cancel our show?
None of them could
believe their ears.
Kaleido Stage was going to
be bought out and dissolved
right after the show.
And the mastermind of Kaleido
Stage's demise was Yuri Killian.
The same Yuri who was once
Layla Hamilton's co-star.
He had been secretly planning
this takeover all along.
With the last show
about to start,
Sora tried to tell
her boss, Kalos,
how she felt about doing
her final performance, but...
I'd like you to know that,
even though this is
our last show, or,
really because this
is our last show,
we're gonna give it
everything we've got.
Is there anything you want me
to say to the cast
before we go on stage?
I guess there's one
thing you can tell them:
If that's how
they think of the show,
it's better not
to go on at all.
Sora could not hide her
agitation after the way
Kalos talked to her.
Shortly after, she
became unable to see me.
Fool? Where are you?
Fool! Where are you hiding?
Don't tell me I can't
see you anymore.
Why won't you come out?
Please, Fool.
I can't believe it;
it happened.
I can't see the Fool anymore.
Listen, if you can see me,
it means that you were
chosen for the stage.
There was a man who was able
to see me but then
he injured himself.
The man that I was just
telling you about gradually
became unable to see me, Sora.
Sora felt like
she'd lost everything,
and she didn't know what to do.
It feels like everything's
slipping away from me,
and I can't get it back.
I don't know what to do.
The thing that finally
cleared up her confusion
was Layla's
unexpected declaration.
I can still talk to your
father if you like, Layla.
I know you don't want this
to be your last performance
at Kaleido Stage.
Today's not going to be
our last show, Yuri.
Huh?
Layla, take a look around you.
It's over.
You may be able to
close Kaleido Stage down,
but don't think that means I'll
never be able to perform again.
This isn't my last show
unless I choose for it to be.
I know that's true, Yuri.
If I didn't believe that,
I don't think I'd have the
heart to go on stage today.
Sora!
I overheard what
you said to Yuri just now.
You really think
today isn't the end!
I was afraid... I'd never get
to be on stage with you again.
But like you said, that won't
happen unless I want it to.
Sora, we have a show to do.
And we don't wanna be
late for the performance.
Right!
It's just...
I don't want to lose.
I've never, not once
in all these years,
had a partner that's
motivated me this much.
Layla?
Where's Sora?
She, uh, messed up
her make-up, and, uh...
She's in there fixing it.
Sora.
Oh, Layla, I'm trying to hurry,
but I just- I don't know how-
I can help you with that.
Let me fix it for you, okay?
But Layla, I can do-
Stop talking, Sora.
I'll be finished in a minute.
I've enjoyed
performing with you.
I wanted to let you know.
But Layla, why would she
say something like that?
This isn't the end.
It can't be, or...
is it?
There. Finished.
Sora, let's go!
Right!
Fool, you-
Here I am.
So you can see me again?
Yeah. Thought I got rid of you.
The Sun!
This card means you should
have hope for tomorrow.
Hope for tomorrow.
That's great!
After this is when our real
performances are gonna start.
So the final
curtain was dropped.
With mixed emotions,
the company members disbursed
to follow their own paths.
It's amazing how quickly
time passes, isn't it?
Two whole weeks,
and in all that time...
They wished for nothing more
than to appear on stage again,
and with that goal in mind,
they began a voluntary
training regimen in addition
to their part-time job.
One for you, one for you,
one for you, one for you.
Meanwhile, Layla followed her
father's wishes by starring
in another film.
They had all gone
their separate ways.
Then one day, Sora, Anna,
and Mia got their chance.
I've found you a job
if you're interested!
Huh?
Good! Here it is.
It says they're looking
for performers at...
Marine Park!
The scale of the
stage was too small,
but they'd still find
a way to perform together.
I've had some
responses to my e-mail.
Really?
And they're all coming!
Let's do a show!
Sora!
It's been so long!
I can't believe you're here.
In this way, the old friends
gathered and formed a new group,
Freedom Rights.
They had practiced hard.
And Sora and her friends
performed beautifully.
Their show was a great success,
but somehow, Sora
couldn't help feeling
that something was missing.
If only Layla could
have been here today.
Hmm?
Just as she thought that...
Hey, Sora. Who is that?
A mysterious
masked star appeared.
She gave a
breathtaking performance.
That scared the pee out of me.
Amazing! She was
only here a minute,
but the crowd's
in the palm of her hand.
Thanks to this mystery
star's death-defying act,
Marine Park was packed,
day after day.
Freedom Rights' performance
was also garnering
favorable reviews.
But one day,
an incident occurred.
Not yet.
It's the masked star!
Finally!
We love you!
A young brother and sister
climbed up a steel tower
in order to have a better
look at the masked star.
Oh!
Those kids are in trouble!
Call the rescue team, quick!
Right.
Melissa, hurry!
The way she moved...
she had to be...
Sora was convinced she knew her.
It's alright, I've got you.
She's gonna crash.
Just hold on to me, okay?
Oh no, I've gotta get back
in control or else
we're both gonna get hurt.
I got ya.
You're okay now.
Somehow, Sora avoided
disaster by working in tandem
with the masked star.
The best part of this
is that Layla wants to be
a part of our company.
With her on our side,
we can make better shows than
we ever did at Kaleido Stage.
It-It's giving me the feeling
that anything is possible.
However, Yuri's unstoppable
evil scheme was to strike Sora
and her friends once more.
Finally, the masked star's
identity was revealed.
After Sora and her friends were
forced to leave Marine Park
due to Yuri's interference,
they decided to participate
in the world performance
festival in Vancouver.
It was their only hope.
It's perfect!
If we raise our
international profile,
the Marine Park will
beg to hire us back.
In the meantime,
Layla was in London,
starring in her latest film.
No, no need to worry.
I'm glad to hear that the
filming is going so smoothly.
This movie success is
extremely important, Layla.
It could make
or break your career.
Yes, I understand, Father.
If we keep on schedule,
we should be filming your final
fight scenes by next week.
I'm looking forward
to seeing them.
Thank you.
The day of the festival arrived.
What is this?
'Z'?
'Z' was an amateur group
from Vancouver who stole
the show from
Sora and her friends
by doing the exact routine that
Freedom Rights had planned.
Our move!
Hey, we do that in our show!
Are they totally copying us?
They were.
This was another one
of Yuri's schemes.
Then their careers will be over.
The audience loves them!
We can't let
those guys beat us!
Freedom Rights was in a bind,
and it was time
for them to go on.
What are we gonna do?
Huh?
Well, if it's an emergency, I
guess we'll have to let you go.
When you come back
for filming next week,
I expect you to be perfect.
The mysterious masked star
appeared once again.
This gave Sora and
her friends the confidence
they needed to go on.
It can't be!
How dare you show up here
without giving us any notice?
I just wanted to thank you
for the flowers, Yuri.
All right.
Just when everyone was convinced
of Freedom Rights' victory...
Don't you get in my way!
Layla!
What are you doing here?
Why aren't you in London
on the film set?
I asked them to
postpone my filming.
You had them do what?
I know you can't
possibly understand this,
but being here was
more important to me.
Until I can perform the perfect
show, I won't be satisfied.
I want to earn the kind of
applause that makes
my whole body tremble!
And for the first time,
I have a partner that
can make that happen.
Layla.
I can't leave this
behind, Father, not yet.
Make sure you get back
to London and finish the
filming as soon as possible.
After that, do what you want.
Layla decided to appear
on stage again with Sora
and the rest of them.
That was when
a miracle occurred.
This?
Can you see me now, Layla?
So, having resolved
to live for the stage,
Layla also became
able to see me.
Layla has always been a
capable performer in the past,
but today you've proven
to be more than that.
And now you're worthy
of all my secrets.
What kind of secrets?
The legendary great maneuver.
No one's attempted it in years.
And the last person who did paid
for the privilege with his life.
But he was not
the first to fall.
Many tried before him,
and many failed.
If you ladies try this,
you will only be the second team
from Kaleido Stage to do so.
Rare that I find two stars
capable of it.
What happened to the other
team from Kaleido Stage?
They died.
But I know... I know
I could do it with you.
That we could do it together.
The place where the two of them
decided to go for special
training was the Grand Canyon.
There was someone
waiting there for them.
The one and only person who knew
the legendary great maneuver.
It's been a while, huh?
Welcome.
Hi, Boss.
Let's get to work.
Sora and Layla's
excruciating training began.
It was beyond anything
the two had imagined.
Sora wasn't sure
she would make it.
Contrary to Layla,
who had steadily managed
to finish their assignments,
it was all Sora could
to just to keep up.
And then...
Layla, wait.
Tell me what I'm doing wrong.
Tell me to work harder,
be stronger!
How can I be a better partner.
I'm sorry, I have
nothing to say.
Sora's determination was shaken
after she was
pushed away by Layla,
a partner in whom
she had put her trust.
Doubting yourself
is just a waste of time.
Either do this or don't try.
But it might be the
best thing for Layla
if I let her choose
a more talented partner.
After Sora lost her confidence,
she headed to Layla's room
with her mind made up.
Layla, I need to talk to you.
Can I come in?
Ken.
Layla isn't in
her room right now.
She went out for a run.
She's gone running?
But it's not light yet.
Layla's trying
to lose some weight.
But why?
Because when you perform
the legendary great maneuver,
you have a much higher chance
of success if both partners
weigh roughly the same.
But that's so dangerous, and
she's doing this because of me?
You need to stop believing
that all the problems in this
partnership are your fault.
Aren't the two of you
supposed to be equal?
Thanks for saying that, Ken.
Layla!
Sora!
I'm so sorry.
I wanted to run away,
because training's so hard.
I told myself I didn't have
what it takes to be
your partner anyway.
But I'm not gonna
doubt myself anymore,
and I'm gonna work extra
hard to catch up with you,
so we can perfect the maneuver
and get Kaleido Stage back.
And I promise Layla,
I won't doubt myself again.
I'll work twice as hard!
I'll be the partner you deserve,
the partner you're
trying to be for me!
No matter what it takes,
I'm not gonna let you down!
We're gonna do the
legendary great maneuver.
I've never doubted for a moment
that you and I would
be able to do this thing.
Huh?
Right.
Both Sora and Layla regained
their trust in each other.
However, fate had new
ordeals in store for them.
Wh-What happened?
Did you hurt yourself?
Due to her drastic
weight loss, Layla became dizzy.
It's nothing, I'm fine.
I guess it's no big deal.
She's doing fine.
Layla was injured.
What cruel fate
awaited them now?
At last it was
time for the show,
but would their
training be enough?
After Layla smashed her
right shoulder in the cliff,
her condition
became much worse.
Her doctor told
her not to perform.
Still, her determination
was not shaken.
Sora and Layla's show.
After overcoming many
harrowing ordeals,
it was finally time for
Sora and Layla to attempt
the legendary great maneuver.
It doesn't look like
they're wearing lifelines.
I don't know.
This is making me nervous.
Are you ready, Sora?
Yes.
Just focus on
what Layla's doing.
Let's do this, Sora.
Jump towards Layla, now!
It's like they both grew
wings. It's incredible!
As long as I can
stay up here with Layla,
I won't ever be afraid.
I'm so happy I feel like crying.
I don't ever want
this moment to end.
I want to keep performing
like this forever.
An absolute faith in life,
one so complete
that it knows no fear.
That is the meaning of the
legendary great maneuver.
Displays such faith in life,
it keeps death at bay.
That's why we thought
it was impossible,
but to find faith
as great as theirs...
Arlon, I think you
must have glimpsed it:
an act so powerful it gives
all who see it new strength.
We'll have to push harder!
I'm ready!
One, two, three!
It was the kind of applause
that Layla had longed for.
The applause that made
her whole body tremble.
However, the price
may have been too great.
I think it is.
There's no way I'll
ever be able to perform
at Kaleido Stage again.
What?
Do you really mean that?
Yes, I do.
Kaleido Stage has lost
the great Layla Hamilton.
Now, what will become
of Sora and her friends?