Hello everyone,
Kaleido Star's about to start,
so make sure that your
room is brightly lit,
and that you're not sitting
too close to the television.
Well, well, well.
We've not seen each
other for a while.
It's Layla.
Did you see the legendary great
maneuver that I did with Sora?
I bet everything on that show,
risking my own fate
and my relationship
with the best
partner I ever had.
Now I'm no longer able to
perform at Kaleido Stage,
but I have no regrets.
Because I found a new dream.
Sora, follow me!
Wow, we've got a whole
week of vacation coming up!
Thank goodness for
annual maintenance!
Yeah, this is my chance
to make the rounds
at all of the comedy clubs.
I'll use my time off
in the library
to plan new productions
for us to do.
I'm gonna spend my days and
nights training on the trapeze.
Sora, would you like to join me?
Huh?
Everyone's so motivated.
You will play Mina Murray.
Oh, yes.
Thank you. Thank you.
If I stay like this, I'll never
be a real Kaleido Star.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
It's nothing at all!
I'm fine, you guys.
Really, I'm fine.
Sora, when you've finished
changing your clothes,
please go to the Boss' office.
He has a surprise for you.
Somehow I have a really
bad feeling about this.
I think you're overreacting.
It's not like he's never made
you work during your vacation.
Just in case,
you should go there
expecting the absolute
worst to happen.
That way the shock
won't feel so bad.
You can handle it, Sora!
Okay.
Huh?
I've been asked to appear
in a show starring Layla!
Are you serious?
Layla recommended you,
but it's during your vacation.
Should I tell them no?
Huh?
Tell 'em that I'll do it!
I'll go to the North Pole!
I'll go to the South Pole!
I'll go anywhere.
Sora is going to appear
on stage with Layla?
I'm gonna see Layla again!
Layla!
"The Ever Amazing Miss Layla."
Excuse me, sir, I'm looking
for an off-Broadway show.
It's called "Salome in Vegas."
Follow that taxi in front of us.
It's Layla.
Sora!
Huh?
Well, Sora, it's been
a long time, hasn't it?
Layla!
Sora.
Hey!
Sora!
Charlotte! Julie!
We're working in the show as
Layla's personal assistants.
Oh wow, Sora, you like
haven't changed at all.
Let me present Kaleido
Stage's Sora Naegino.
This is our producer,
Mike Abbott.
Hi there.
I look forward to working
with you this week.
I look forward to
working with you, too!
And, standing up
here on the stage
is the writer and
director of our show.
This is Cathy Taymor.
Hello there.
It's nice to meet
you Miss Taymor.
Ah!
Hmm, yes, I think the
costume will fit her.
You see, our dear Layla
fired the previous performer.
Uh, she was fired?
She was a good performer
with a respectable career.
But it seems Layla
didn't like her.
Layla fired her in the middle
of a live performance
without consulting the
director or the producer.
Is that professional behavior?
Uh...
No, it's not professional!
Cathy, I refuse
to appear on stage
with anyone who isn't
driven to do their best.
You spoiled rich girls
are such a pain.
Lucky for us we could book her,
because her schedule
happened to be open.
But what were you planning to do
if we couldn't find a
replacement for the role?
--Well, maybe-
--Thank you for coming, Sora.
Uh, thanks.
But I can only appear in
your show for one week,
and then I have to
return to Kaleido Stage.
That'll be fine.
We'll figure out the
rest when the time comes,
so don't worry about it.
Oh, okay.
You're only in one scene,
but it's one of the
most important scenes
in the entire show.
This is the scene in which
Salome dances in the
back half of the stage.
Got it.
Anger and sorrow. Love and hate.
All of Salome's passion
is poured into this scene.
And I want you to fire up
those emotions by playing
the shadowy representation
of my character's psyche,
and raise the temperature
of the stage.
Raise the temperature.
Once we choreograph the rough
outline of your routine,
the way you perform it
will be left up to you.
In other words,
you're free to ad-lib.
You want me to ad-lib?
Alright Sora, let's run
through the basic outline.
Okay.
Hold on!
That sounds like...
It's May!
Who are you?
Hello, Layla,
my name is May Wong.
I've always been
inspired by you,
and earlier this year,
I joined Kaleido Stage
and scored higher
than any new entrant.
Why are you here?
This is for you.
Thank you.
So then, you're the one
who was chosen to be
Leon Oswald's partner in the
new Kaleido Stage production.
Yes. I beat out Sora in the
competition for the role.
So instead of Sora,
you should choose me to
be your partner on stage.
What?
Rolling Flower!
How did May find out I was
invited here by Layla?
And why did she come to
New York planning to do this?
Shining Flower!
Miracle Great!
That's enough, May! Stop it!
I won't!
You weren't the
one invited here.
So get off the stage, now!
You were invited to
appear in the show,
because Layla didn't know
that a person of my
talent was available.
Wow, looks like
this new hot shot
might be some real competition.
Like Sora doesn't
stand a chance.
Wouldn't it be
interesting to put
both of them on stage, Layla?
Both of them on stage?
I think that's a good idea.
All right, let's
start rehearsal.
Yeah, that's right,
we need another costume.
Well?
I think the scene needs
just one more idea.
But we can work it out tomorrow.
Ladies, please come with me.
I was able to get you the last
room at the Century Hotel.
You're putting me in
the same room as Sora?!
Well, yeah. I am.
I refuse!
May, don't be a prima donna.
I'd rather sleep outside
than have to share
the same room with you!
Oh yeah, well who'd
wanna stay with you?
Stop your whining!
You two should be saving your
energy for tomorrow's show!
Uh, yes ma'am.
Perhaps there is
another solution.
You could cancel the hotel
and come stay at my place.
Well, this is it.
Wow.
Amazing.
--Look at New York City.
--It's beautiful!
Make yourselves at home.
I'll try to make us some coffee.
Try to make?
Miss Layla, that's the place
where you pour in the water.
And the coffee beans
have to be ground first.
Oh, I forgot.
If you made coffee more often,
you'd remember how to make it.
Thank goodness
you're here to help me.
Oh, I'm so honored to be
of use to you, Miss Layla.
You know I always love to help.
Layla has started
a brand new life.
On a new stage, in a new city.
I wonder if the
legendary great maneuver
is already nothing more than
a distant part of her past.
Wouldn't it be
interesting to put
both of them on stage, Layla?
Both of them on stage?
I think that's a good idea.
It seems that I'm not the
only one she has hopes for.
Sora, would you
quit moping already?
Moping?
Now that both of us are
going to be in the show,
you'll have to pull
yourself together
if you don't want to
embarrass Layla on the stage.
I had so many things I wanted
to talk with Layla about,
but it looks like I won't get
that chance because of you!
Layla isn't your
private property!
For your information,
I wanna talk to Layla, too!
And it was always my dream to
appear on the stage with her.
I came here so Layla would
know I'm better than you.
And see I can achieve things
far beyond your abilities.
I will not lose to a
performer so incompetent
that she injured Layla on stage.
Wait just a second.
Did you just say that
Sora injured me?
If Sora hadn't been your partner
on the legendary great maneuver,
I'm certain you would have
never been injured, Layla.
Why don't both of
you have a seat?
I was injured because
I wasn't concentrating
on what I needed to be doing.
Even though I
smashed my shoulder,
I attempted the legendary
great maneuver.
I did it of my own free will.
So it would be wrong
for you to blame Sora.
Of course, as a result,
I can no longer do
that kind of performance.
However, on the bright
side of things,
I find myself looking
at a new opportunity.
Layla, if you had never
injured your shoulder,
right now you would be in
even more spectacular shows.
I chose to go on stage
and perform that show.
What?
After I performed the
legendary great maneuver,
and people heard that
I wouldn't be able
to go back to Kaleido Stage,
I received a lot of job offers
to be in movies and plays
and television shows.
But after accomplishing
something like
the legendary great maneuver,
I didn't feel
interested in anything.
And then...
You-You have a visitor.
Thank you for seeing me.
Here's the script.
And if I might ask, when
will your injury be healed?
To recover any range
of motion in my arm
will probably take
about a month.
I would be grateful if you could
find a way to recover faster.
But I guess I'll have to wait.
So why don't we team up?
You won't regret it.
"Salome in Vegas"?
Everything about it was fresh.
Yes, there were some people
who murmured that I had
fallen in the world,
because I was
willing to appear in
an off-Broadway show
that wasn't very big.
But things like that
have never bothered me.
And I paid no attention to them.
Because in that show,
I had once again found
something that motivated me.
And that's when I knew that
this stage would be my new home.
And I also knew then that
Cathy would be my new partner.
So you now consider
Cathy to be your partner?
I do.
Layla, I will do my
very best on stage,
to prove to you that I
should also be considered
as your partner.
I have always
dreamed that one day
I would appear
on stage with you.
And what's your
dream after that?
Wha-What?
My dream after that dream?
I'm curious,
because your current dream
will come true tomorrow.
You're right.
I guess I was preoccupied
with beating Sora,
so I never thought about it.
So it's really true then, Layla?
Your current dream is here, huh?
Sora.
That's right.
You haven't touched
my coffee at all.
Disgusting.
And I also knew then that
Cathy would be my new partner.
I'm no longer Layla's partner.
I know that.
Since Layla left Kaleido Stage,
and we started walking
on different paths,
it's natural that
things would change.
I know that.
But still, I never
expected to hear it
said so clearly straight
from Layla's mouth.
I never expected I would
feel so totally alone,
just hearing Layla
utter those words.
When it comes down to it,
I can't stand on my own,
even a little bit.
It's so pathetic!
This isn't good.
I can't perform tomorrow
feeling like this.
I have to pull myself together.
Layla's constellation is Leo,
which emits a blinding light.
And hidden in its shadow
is Sora's Sagittarius,
who's lost sight of the target
at which it should be aiming.
I wouldn't worry about anything.
Just perform the role
however you feel like it.
Okay.
Stop looking at me with
those puppy dog eyes.
I want you to get on the
stage with enough spirit
to steal the part
of Salome from me.
Salome, please
come dance for me!
I don't want to dance right now.
Herron, I think my heart
might be the only thing in
the whole country that doesn't
do exactly as you please.
Salome.
Johann, your skin is so white
it's like new-fallen snow,
and your lips are so soft...
Salome, don't ever
touch me again!
Johann!
Johann...
I love you.
I want you to get on the
stage with enough spirit
to steal the part
of Salome from me.
Stand-by.
Herron, I will
dance for you now.
But in return, I want
you to grant my wish!
Now, the match begins.
Steal the audience's eyes.
Intimidate me!
In order to meet
Layla's expectations...
I'll have to give a performance
that's even better than Layla's.
Layla!
I want to be acknowledged.
I won't lose to May.
I won't lose to Sora.
I will win no matter what!
I'll make sure I win!
This is great!
But...
I just cannot beat Layla.
Ask me for anything your
heart desires, Salome.
There is but only one
thing I want, Herron.
So, this is what you want, huh?
I do.
Layla shines so supremely
up there on that stage.
But no matter what I do, I can't
catch up with her at all.
We couldn't even match the
performance that Layla gave.
Mmm.
Thank you for coming this week.
Thanks to you, the show
was a great success.
Was it really?
Really. Because of you,
Cathy finally understands
what I'm talking about
when I say there's not
enough fire on the stage.
You mean...that's the reason
you invited me here?
Yes, I thought you
could help me show Cathy
what a fiery stage was like,
but you've changed, Sora.
When I was still
performing at Kaleido Stage,
I was always fearful
that you would
come up from behind
and surpass me.
But this time around,
I didn't feel any
kind of competitive edge
from you out there at all.
When times get rough,
you're the only person
who can save yourself.
What you're aiming for in life,
what you're hoping to grasp...
The only one who knows is you.
The answer to all of these
are to be found inside of you.
I will find my current dream
on this stage in New York.
Of course, I still have my
dream for Kaleido Stage,
and it's very important to me.
I'm putting all my
faith in you, Sora,
because I know you have what it
takes to be a true Kaleido Star.
Layla!
Go after your dream,
and don't let yourself get lost.
If you do that,
the road to becoming a Kaleido
Star will appear for you.
Going after my dream...
That's right, just
keep going, Sora.
I will.
Say hello to everyone
at Kaleido Stage for me.
--Yes.
--Yes! Don't worry.
I'll take care of it for you!
Fool!
I can still see you.
I admit I didn't understand
your relationship with Layla,
but don't get the wrong idea.
We're still competitors.
Yeah, I understand.
Still, I wonder what
I wanna do now.
The answer is inside me.
I don't want my dad
looking sad like that.
And so, we decided to do
a kids show at Kaleido Stage.
Wow, Marion is really
good at the trampoline!
I'm not doing the trampoline!
Are you gonna bury your dream
with your mother's memories?
I wanna bring back
a smile to Marion's face.
I want to! I want to! I want to!
Next time on Kaleido Star:
"Marion's Amazing Debut."
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky.