Everyone, Kaleido Star
is about to start.
So make sure that your
room is brightly lit
and that you're not
sitting too close to the TV.
Well, well, well. Hello
everyone, I'm Yuri Killian.
Today is the day the Circus
Festival will take place.
On this day, three years ago,
I was here with Layla.
We were the winners.
And our glory started from here.
This time, my partner is Sora.
There's no way I can erase
the mistakes made in the past.
But this time I'll do
everything in my power
for Sora, Layla,
and Kaleido Stage.
Still, I wonder if Sora really
can endure this cruel stage.
Too slow.
Too early this time!
"Cruel Amazing Festival."
The school Yuri's attending...
should be around here, but...
Ah! There he is.
Why don't we stop here today?
No, not yet.
Okay, then, one more hour.
Then let's end today's training.
Resting is another
part of practice.
Okay.
Oh! This must be
the practice room
for the school Yuri's attending.
What kind of maneuver
are they working on?
It doesn't matter.
I'm just glad Sora's safe.
Alice, Mute, you were a big
help today with training.
Thank you so much.
Oh, you're welcome.
Can we come tomorrow as well?
Oh, no! You don't have to...
We learned a lot from watching
you. Please, let us help.
Is it okay with you?
They're nice enough
to offer their help.
It would be impolite to
say no, don't you think?
Yeah, that's true.
Okay, please come and help us.
This is great.
Okay, see you tomorrow then.
Right. Have a good night.
Good night.
Sora, I'll walk you
to the hotel.
Well, I don't have a hotel.
What?
Then, you could
stay at my place.
I could? But that would
be asking too much of you.
Hi, Sora! What a surprise!
What are you doing here?
I-I was taking a walk.
Taking a walk?
But you're out of breath.
Are you okay?
Anyway, if you need
a place to stay,
I'll help you find one.
Well, but I...
It's no trouble for you
to stay at my place.
No, Sora has a family.
She's part of the cast
of Kaleido Stage.
And Kaleido Stage
will look after her.
Thank you for everything!
Get a good night's sleep.
Okay.
Qui, a room is available.
Oh, good. Sora,
you've got a room.
Really? Thank you so much, Ken.
Then, shall we charge
the room to Kaleido Stage?
No. Charge it to me,
Ken Robbins.
And please keep this
a secret from her.
Can you do that?
Qui.
The angel's maneuver.
I'll perfect it. I will.
And I'm going to win.
So let me see.
I guess the ones I need to watch
out for are Mr. and Mrs. Patlowa
and street performers
Mute and Alice.
Well, that's no big deal.
My Demon Spiral is
absolutely perfect.
Leon and I will
win this for sure.
What is this?
I'm going to compete with
the world's top stars,
my maneuver against theirs.
But I'm not quite fired up.
Something's missing.
I wonder what.
Don't try to jump so hard.
Okay.
Feel out the moment
when your body's been
given the most force...
and then jump!
And maintain a beautiful
pose as you go up.
You're an angel!
Sora, do you know
you have a weak point?
Yeah, I know. Ken has talked
to me about it before.
My body's unbalanced
because I've only been
doing big maneuvers.
But I'm trying to get stronger.
I know.
But even with only
the kind of basics
they teach at circus school,
you shouldn't be losing
your balance this much.
I don't get it.
Oh. In Japan, there aren't
really any circus schools,
so I never went to one.
Huh? Really?
I can't believe she
was able to do
the legendary great maneuver...
But I'll work hard.
I'll endure it no matter how
tough this thing gets.
This is the "Angel's maneuver."
It's supposed to give the
impression of weightless,
just like the feathers
of an angel's wings.
It's not an easy
maneuver to perform.
Just like a ballerina,
you have to maintain
a beautiful pose
and make your body seem
as light as a feather.
You need a strong
grounding in the basics.
I may not have all
the basics, that's true.
But I endured Leon's
special training!
No matter how tough it was,
I managed to get through it.
So I'll cover for
my lack of the basics
with sheer will power!
Please, Yuri! I can do this!
Sora, when it's you saying it,
I start to feel
like you really can.
All right. Let's continue
the practice then.
Okay!
I have to get the
timing just perfect.
And I have to pose beautifully.
What this?! What does it mean?
Why is Sora on the list
of those registered?
And her partner's Yuri.
I see. He was her
way to get in here.
So she still hasn't
given up on victory.
Hmm. Interesting.
Now I know...
I know what was missing
from the festival.
Sora, it was you!
Fool, try to knock me
down by crashing into me!
Yippee!
Please aim for my back.
What? Aim for your back?
And I was this close, too.
Why can't I ever get a break?
Yes!
Too fast!
Too slow! Pay more attention!
Okay!
Demon Spiral!
Her move, it has changed.
What's this feeling inside?
I can hardly wait
for the festival.
I want to compete in it.
I want to compete in it now!
I want to compete... with Sora.
Don't forget to pose!
O-Okay!
In only a few days,
she managed to reach this point.
Impressive.
Now, if she can just maintain
that beautiful pose...
Amazing. I've never seen
that maneuver before.
It really looks like
an angel's wings.
I can do this!
The day is finally here.
When everything
will be determined.
Sora!
Yo-hoo, Sora!
Mia, Sarah, I can't believe
you came. Where's Anna?
Huh?
Un, deux, trois.
Un chien!
Mr. Charlie.
He's the real thing!
She's off seeing the clown
she admires, Mr. Charlie.
Anna looks happy.
--It's been awhile, Yuri.
--Yeah.
Thanks for coming. The trip
must have been expensive.
Don't worry about
our travel expenses.
Sarah negotiated
that with Kalos.
--Kaleido Stage is paying.
--What? R-Really?
So I'm only one paying
out of my own pocket?
Well, there's nothing
I can do now.
Sora, be sure to win!
So we can be together in the
festival three years from now.
If I've told you once,
I've told you a thousand times!
How can I do this if
you're throwing your legs
all over the place?
Just hold very still.
Agh! I forgot to bring
my good luck pendant!
I'm done for.
Ouch!
What are you doing?!
Oh, I didn't know
you were there.
Hey, you guys,
that's Yuri Killian.
But I thought he...
He should have stayed retired.
The partner he's with. She's...
Isn't she the girl who
paired with Layla Hamilton
and did the legendary
great maneuver...
Yeah, that's right.
They're a real big shot pair.
This stinks, if you ask me.
Sora.
May...
Hi there, Sora.
I see you don't know
when to give up either.
We're going to win!
There's no way we'll
lose to the both of you!
Well, I can't wait to see that.
Leon...
Yuri Killian...
Yeah. Long time, no see.
What? Do you two
know each other?
Did you meet when
you participated
in the festival three years ago?
Leon...?
Who ever thought we would see
each other at this place again?
Perhaps a match with you is
my unavoidable destiny, Leon.
In that case, do you
want to partner with me?
With me as I am now,
the God of Death?
Well now, you have changed.
I learned from you.
Or have you forgotten that?
You taught me what
I needed to do
to climb to the top
in this world.
You should place more value
on your current partner.
What's going on?
Did something happen
between Yuri and Leon?
Does it involve the
festival three years ago?
I... don't know. I don't know.
Oh, you may not have heard this,
so I guess I should tell you.
Layla is here at the show.
Really?
Yeah, she is.
As a trophy presenter to the
winners of the competition.
What do you think, Sora?
Which one of us will be
receiving the trophy from Layla?
And now, for the opening of this
International Circus Festival,
please listen to a few words
from one of the previous
winners, Miss Layla Hamilton!
Welcome to the International
Circus Festival.
This can be a very cruel place.
But unless we overcome it,
there's a step forward
we cannot take.
So if you want to take that
first step toward your dream,
you have to give this
everything you've got.
Sorry, sorry. My hand slipped.
But I see they don't call you
the God of Death for nothing.
Your partners may get destroyed,
but you're certainly won't be.
Entry No.5, Mr. &amp; Mrs. Patlowa.
Ah, would you look at them!
Mr. and Mrs. Patlowa
are so happily married.
Soon, it'll be May
and Leon's turn.
Then after that,
it'll be Mute and Alice.
And then, Sora's turn comes up.
Oh... This is more
nerve wracking
than when I'm in
the competition.
I know, I know.
Sora, do you want some water?
Oh, thank you.
Hey, what's wrong?
Well... Mute and Alice
should have been here by now.
I wonder if anything's happened.
I wonder where they are.
Don't worry about other people.
Just leave them alone.
But, May...
They helped me practice
for the festival every day.
If something happened
to them because of that...
Oh, did you really exploit
your rivals' goodwill?
For you, that's
not half bad, Sora.
You're wrong. I would never
do something like that.
Don't pretend to be
a Goody Two-Shoes.
In the end, it's the same
as if you intended
to use them, isn't it?
It'd be nice if they just
didn't show up at all.
Let's go.
Okay.
I never meant for
that to happen.
I'll just check.
Maybe they're out there.
--No.
--Huh?
Leave them alone.
Yuri...
They'll be here.
What?
Sorry for being late.
We're No. 8, Mute and Alice.
All right then. Go to the
waiting room and get ready.
They made it.
Mute and Alice, I was so
worried. I'm glad you made--
Uh... Your costumes are nice.
You... You both
look like angels.
Yes, that's right.
So if you'll excuse us now,
we'll be doing the angel's
maneuver before you do.
You used us.
So don't you think it's
only fair we do the same?
But I... I never meant...
Did you think we were
helping you out of
the goodness
of our hearts?
We have to make
everyone's dream come true.
We can't lose.
I hope you understand.
We did nothing against
the rules. You can check.
Sora, are you all right?
Yeah. I'm all right.
It was just...
Well... I got a little
sick, that's all.
Oh, but... I think I'm...
I'm fine now. Really...
I told you.
Don't screw up the timing!
I did it right!
If we can't win this year,
we don't have another chance.
I already know that.
Honestly. I hate
the Kaleido Stage.
After Layla Hamilton retired,
I thought we would have a shot.
But no, they had to send
two pairs this year.
Oh! You're here.
All we have now are the
pieces of a broken dream.
All thanks to you.
I hope you're happy.
Nobody's wrong, Sora.
This is just that kind of world.
You were prepared for
this, weren't you?
Yeah.
It's almost time to go.
Okay.
This can be a very cruel place.
But unless we overcome it,
there's a step forward
we cannot take.
And if I want to take that
first step toward my dream...
Demon! Spiral!
What kind of maneuver is this?!
Can he grab her?
It's impossible.
More amazing than before.
Listen. The hall is dead silent.
Everyone's been
enchanted by a demon.
A demon.
What is this? I feel
out of place here.
Like I don't belong.
The applause should
be the same as always.
But I'm afraid to win it
this time. I'm afraid...
During practice,
we almost perfected this.
We'll perfect it here.
We can do it!
Angel's maneuver?
No, this isn't even close
to Angel's maneuver.
Alice!
Mute. Hold on!
I screwed up.
Mute...
Mute.
We've never had
to imitate anyone.
We were proud to do own work.
But then you came along,
and we couldn't just let you--
Stop it, Alice. Sorry, Sora.
We want to win the festival
and get the world's attention.
But it's not only for ourselves.
If we win, we'll organize
a performance team
with these guys right here.
That's our dream.
That's right. So if
you'll excuse us now,
we'll be doing the angel's
maneuver before you do.
In the end, it's the same
as if you intended to
use them, isn't it?
All we have now are the
pieces of a broken dream.
All thanks to you.
Is this it?
No, no. This isn't the
place I was aiming for.
This isn't the place at all.
The place I'm aiming for is...
The stage I saw with
mother and father.
It was more fun.
It was happy, and...
I'm so sorry, Layla. Sorry.
I should never have come here.
She's not coming down.
She's just floating.
The angel's maneuver.
Yes, I think I've
heard of it before.
Angel's maneuver?
Sora! Give me your hands.
Will you be able to go on?
Sorry. I can't do it.
Sora...
What?
She's going to quit?
Sora. Is she crying?
Hey, isn't that
the Angel's maneuver?
I've never seen it done.
I didn't know the Kaleido Stage
had that kind of talent.
I wonder why she quit
in the middle of it.
If she did it all the way,
she might have won.
Mastering the angel's
maneuver to that extent...
Come in.
Uh... Layla... I, I'm sorry.
I can't believe you withdrew.
You're the worst.
You disgraced the festival.
You ran away from the stage.
A serious match
was taking place.
I'm disappointed in you, Sora.
I'm so sorry.
I thought I wanted
to take Layla's path.
I thought it could
take me to my dream.
But now, I don't know anymore.
What do I want?
What should I aim for?
Sora, do you really intend
to just end things like this?
And so, I ended up
coming back to Japan.
I'm getting to catch up
with my old friends.
I can't believe you, Sora.
You could have at least called
to tell me that you're in town.
A loving family.
Welcome back, Sora.
This is... This is fine.
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Amazing and Sad Homecoming."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...