Hey, everyone, Kaleido
Star's about to start,
so make sure that your room
is brightly lit and that you're
not sitting too close to the TV.
Well well well. Do you have
any friends that like to
make people laugh? Anna
says her Father used to
make her laugh a lot when
she was little, but it's been
so long since she's seen him
that he doesn't even seem like
the same person anymore.
And now it looks like she
never wants to see him again.
I wonder if there's anything
I can do to help her out?
I wonder, I wonder...
Anna's Not So Amazing Father.
Wow, Anna, you're
getting quite a fan base.
Sounds like you've
got more every day.
Hey, maybe you should go to the
lobby and say hello to them,
you think?
I'm just about ready.
What? It's too much?
It's way too much.
You'll terrify them.
I guess I've still
got a lot to learn.
Hey, Anna? How come
you joined Kaleido Stage?
I mean, instead of
being a comedian?
Because I love Kaleido Stage.
Just as much as I love comedy.
I get it. You wanna use the
stage to make people laugh.
Well if that was your goal,
you and Sora've
already made that happen!
What's wrong?
'Standup comedian Jack Baron
will be at the Comedy Theatre
this week only.'
I've never heard of him.
Is he really good or something?
I don't know. I haven't
talked to him in ten years.
Oh, you know this guy?
Jack Baron he's my father.
Really?
No! Bacchus, let go!
Give it back!
Give me back my shoe!
Return Anna's shoe or suffer
the revenge of the Frog-People.
He used to do this thing where
he imitated a frog or an owl,
and it used to always
make me and my friends laugh.
Anna, I must speak to you.
Who are you supposed to be?
Well I don't tell anyone,
but I'm an alien from
a star called Jaga Imo.
And my name is Jaga Imo jaga.
Stop playing with those potatoes
so I can finish dinner.
You got me in trouble jaga.
But then one day...
But why, Jack?
Please, try to understand...
You're leaving us?
If I stay here like
this I'll be ruined.
Daddy? Daddy! See you tonight!
Come home early, okay?
But he didn't come back. That
was the last time I saw him.
You see, my Dad's agent promised
that that he was gonna get my
Dad his very own television
series. But I guess none of that
ever worked out for him.
Well that's show biz, right?
You haven't seen him
at all in ten years?
Nope, not even once. Every
once in a while he'll send me
a Christmas card. I've
written him a few times, too,
but he's always moved before
my letters could get to him.
So that's why you're always
checking the listings for
the Comedy Theatre. You
never know when your Father
might come to town again.
Well yeah, maybe that's
one reason for it,
but I do really love comedy and
I like knowing who's in town.
Hey, uh isn't that theatre
really close to us you guys?
Well?
Right. We should go see his act.
I don't know, you guys,
part of me wants to see my Dad,
but part of me is scared.
Then we'll accompany you,
Your Highness!
Quit it! I told you to stop
putting your hand in my back!
Why are you just sitting there?!
He's trying to kill me!
This is exciting!
Will your dad recognize you?
Oh, I'm sure he will.
He's gonna be so surprised!
Oh, you're too kind.
Hey, thank the nice folks,
then get off stage.
Right. Thank you very much.
Hey, use your own voice,
you moron!
Now it's time for our next
act, and the show can only
get better, right?
Just kidding, folks!
Ladies and gentlemen, please
welcome to the stage the one,
the only, Jack Baron!
That last guys been using the
same material for twenty years.
The only thing that's different
is he's got less hair and
the puppet's got
a full set of dentures.
But then again,
I guess the audiences
have gone downhill, too.
What's wrong?
You guys don't look like
you're having too much fun.
You two on a date or something?
Yeah.
The girl you brought in
yesterday was way hotter.
What are you talking about?
I wasn't here yesterday!
It isn't true.
I wouldn't worry about it too
much. At least you're skinnier
than the girl he
brought in here yesterday.
No, wait!
Are you happy now?
Hey, thanks for the beer.
I was getting a little thirsty.
Daddy! Daddy!
So we've got a
celebrity here tonight:
the Little Mermaid
from Kaleido Stage.
What? Oh, I-- uh, hello!
I always thought mermaids
were half woman, half fish.
But this one looks more
like she's half whale, folks.
But seriously, people,
it's a sweet little story.
It reminds us that even
the chunkiest little mermaid
can fall in love, too.
How can this person be my Dad?
You're adorable, Anna.
There's my girl.
Let's go.
Daddy...
Watch out folks, 'cause before
you know it Kaleido Stage
is gonna turn into
a seafood restaurant.
Anna?
Anna, wait a second!
Looks like everyone's
in a hurry to get out of here.
Is there a fire drill
no one told me about?
It looks like Jack Baron's
still got one fan he
hasn't chased away yet.
Jack, you've gotta come
to New York.
You'll never be a big-time
name if you stay out here.
Hey, Daddy, where are
you going? Daddy?
Daddy!
Hey watch it buddy!
He lied to me.
How'd it look out here?
Another great show, Anna.
I'm glad last night
didn't throw you off.
Yeah, I'm sorry about that,
making you feel bad and all.
So are you gonna try to see your
Dad while he's still in town?
Uh no I think it'll be better
if I don't see him again.
What? But why?
Because ten years ago Jack Baron
walked out on my Mom and me
and he never looked back.
He's made it pretty clear
that he doesn't want
anything to do with me.
Anna...
She'll never be a comedian
if she's that nice.
Maybe we should go back-- uh?
Come back!
Sora!
Huh?
Wait, Mr. Baron!
Come back here!
Excuse me.
Stop running from me!
What'd you do to Sora?
No! It isn't what you think!
What, is this revenge
for yesterday?
No. I just wanted
to talk to you is all.
You were there to see
Anna, weren't you?
I just happened to be taking
a stroll in the neighborhood.
Anna's talked a lot about you.
How you used to do
those silly voices.
She said you always knew
how to make her feel better
when she was a little girl.
And then she said,
'Yeah, he used to be great
even though now he's
just a washed-up hack.'
That's not true.
Just face it: she's better off
without a dad like me.
Figured you'd be thirsty
after runnin' like that.
No.
Oh, wait. How much longer
are you going to be in town?
I leave tomorrow. Right after
the last show of the night.
But that's so soon.
I'm only at the Comedy Theatre
'cause the owner felt sorry
for me. Don't wanna
overstay my welcome, do I?
Now would you take
a look at that card?
Yet again a silly girl
is poking her nose in where
it doesn't belong.
You've shown me that card
before and it doesn't mean
that at all, so quit it.
And all this time I thought
you were ignoring me.
This is the inverted Moon.
It foretells that someone
will acknowledge his
shortcomings and finally start
moving in the right direction
for the first time in years.
Right. It sounds to me like
there's not a better time to
get Anna and her
father back together.
You know, your father's going to
be leaving town tomorrow night.
Oh, no!
My shirt shrunk!
Hey, Anna what do you
think about going
to the comedy club tonight?
I'm not sure. I think... I'll
go for a poached egg today.
Uh. You know, your father
told me he'd be eating in
the restaurant on the pier
before his shows this afternoon.
Will you meet him there?
Sora you do realize that
everyone in the cast has
been gossiping about Anna's
father for days now, right?
Maybe it would be better
if you left this alone.
So they wouldn't have
any more to talk about.
Hi, do you need a table?
Mr. Baron? Uh I know you weren't
expecting to see me here,
but I...
I understand.
You're here to say Anna
doesn't want to see me, right?
Uh. I I'm so sorry about this.
You know, I think maybe if
I'd stopped pressuring her
and minded my own business, Anna
would've decided to come here
and meet you on her own.
Anna must be very lucky
to have a friend who
cares about her like you do.
Well I'm not so sure of that.
You see, I also lost
my Father and my Mother
when I was a child.
And I know that I'd give
anything to see them again.
I figured since Anna had the
chance to see her father...
But I was wrong.
I wasn't doing any of this for
Anna, I was doing it for myself.
I'm so sorry for this.
What's wrong with me?
Don't cry anymore,
Little Mermaid.
You look better
when you're smiling.
When Anna was a little girl
that little trick always
used to make her laugh.
My mermaid friend here needs
a giant bowl of ice cream.
Hello?
Mom it's me.
Anna! How are you, sweetheart?
Fine. What are you up to?
Oh, I was about just going to
try to fix the window that
Bacchus broke this morning.
You still there?
Is something wrong?
I saw Dad again.
You did?
Yeah. He was playing
at the Comedy Theatre here.
The Comedy Theatre?
You know the place?
Of course. I used to
go there all the time.
In fact, that's where
your father and I met.
It is?
I worked there as a waitress,
and one day a guy came in
wanting to be a comedian.
Bob, the owner,
decided to give him a chance.
After that, Jack became a
regular at the Comedy Theatre.
He was warmhearted and funny.
He really was one-of-a-kind,
and everyone loved him.
He was our most popular act.
And I guess you could say he was
pretty popular with me, too.
But he's really changed.
How?
He spent his whole act making
the audience mad at him.
That's not comedy!
That's just mean...
Did you say that to Jack?
What?
Did you tell him how you felt?
If he's that bad the only person
who can make him see it is you.
I think he'll listen.
Tell him hello for me
when you see him.
Thank you! Thank you!
Okay, folks, keep that
applause going for Jack Baron
for his last Cape Mary
performance!
Go out there and
knock 'em dead, Jackie.
I was afraid Anna wouldn't come.
Guess she's just
not ready to forgive him.
Huh. So you guys stuck around
for that? I guess you dimwits
need to get your ventriloquism
fix somewhere since they
don't play that crap on TV.
What!
Hm? Hey, those are
some sweet looking glasses.
But they're not as nice as mine.
See? That's much better!
I put my glasses on and I don't
have to see your
girlfriend's face anymore.
Why don't you come down here
and say that again?
Not again...
Well, well, well. Nobody seems
to be enjoying your show.
What do you think you're doing?
Anna! It's you!
Anna!
Well this is a surprise.
You're just like your mother,
you know that? But then
again your mom's about
twice as good looking
as you are...
You know, Dad for a big
comedian you sure don't
make the audience
laugh much, do you?
Looks like you're more Junk
Baron than Jack Baron anymore.
Good one, Jack Baron the
junk baron. That could be
a great stage name for me...
And that reminds me:
didn't you go to New York
to make a name for yourself?
So, what, you're so big
you can only play the club
you started out in?
Ten years ago my agent told me
I'd be playing in the biggest
venues the U.S. had to offer.
How could I say no to that?
And so Jack Baron abandoned his
family to find fame and fortune.
And it's thanks to that agent
that I got to make a tour of
all the comedy clubs in
New York where I begged them
to let me perform.
How come your agent
wasn't doing that for you?
He had a heavy drinking schedule
to maintain with my money.
What?
I was turned down by all
the finest comedy clubs
New York City had to offer,
and then I was turned down
by all the seediest ones.
Huh. I guess even the
seedy clubs had levels
of professionalism
to maintain.
I'd been in the city about
a month when I came back to
my filthy little motel room and
discovered that my agent had
run off with my money and
all my stuff. I'll never find
another agent as
honest as he was...
Wait, if all that stuff happened
just a few weeks after you
left Mom and me, then why
in the world didn't you just
come back home?
Hey, I lost my shirt, Anna,
I couldn't come home like that.
So I kept looking for it in
underpasses and alleyways
and dumpsters
behind posh hotels...
It's kinda funny after all this
time here I am performing again
and still there's only one
person I want to make laugh.
Daddy!
No matter how long
I stayed away there was only
one person's laughter
I ever wanted to hear.
Then what the heck
are you waiting for, Dad?
You're a comedian, aren't you?
Come on, make your beautiful
daughter laugh again, Jack.
Jack, here!
Remember me?
You're adorable, Anna.
Anna? Please don't cry. If you
start crying now sweetheart
I just don't know what I'll do.
Anna...
Dad...
What do you think about
hitting the road with me?
That might be great someday
but I'm happy here right now.
I see.
What are you going
to do now, Mr. Baron?
Bob got me a gig at
a comedy club in St. Louis,
so I'll be up there for about a
week. Looks like Jack Baron's
career isn't over
yet after all, huh Anna?
So long.
Hey, Dad?
Good luck out there okay?
Oh, and Mom says hi.
Thanks. I'll see you soon...
There goes my Dad, Jack Baron.
The same Jack Baron who used to
make me laugh when
I was a little girl.
Why does that silly girl
bother me so much?
Uh-oh, it looks like there's
gonna be some trouble again.
Now we have to walk
the tightrope?!
Over a pit of flames?!
But this could be my big
chance to costar with Layla.
I won't be intimidated.
I won't, I won't, I won't!
Next time on Kaleido Star, 'An
Amazingly Hot New Production.'
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...