Hello, everyone,
Kaleido Star is about to start.
So please make sure that
your room is brightly lit
and that you aren't sitting
too close to the television.
Well, well, well.
Have you ever tried really
hard at something even though
you weren't sure you'd succeed?
Seems like I'm always
doing stuff like that...
But this time I think
I'm in way over my head.
I mean, Layla's just so amazing.
But we're about
to open our show,
and I'm not going
to let her down now.
I'm not, I'm not!
No Sora, that
wasn't fast enough.
I know. I'm sorry.
Can we try it again?
All right, get back up here.
That routine is so hard.
I know.
All right!
Sorry, Layla.
I was too early with that.
One, two, three!
One, two three--
Sorry!
They've got less than a week
to go before the show opens.
I know, and Sora's
way too freaked out
about the timing of this thing.
She's so worried about getting
it perfect she messes it up.
'The Amazing Competition
Calls Up A Storm.'
I don't know what Kalos
was thinking on this one.
I mean, your performance styles
mix about as well as oil
and water, Layla.
On the other hand, all of
this could be part of some
publicity stunt that he's
dreamed up. What if he's
just using the two of you?
One thing's certain:
to succeed you're going to have
to perform at Sora's pace.
If she wants to
keep playing leads,
then she should perform at mine.
Right...
One, two, three!
One, two, three--
Not your most graceful.
I just can't seem
to get the timing right.
If I stay with
Layla I'm too slow,
but if I do my own
thing I'm too fast.
I've just gotta find
some way to match her...
Sora?
Yes?
You have a guest.
Huh? I'm not
expecting anyone... Yes?
But, Layla what are you--
I'll leave you kids to it.
Thank you.
Yeah, okay. So what's up?
I'm going to be staying
with you. If you don't mind.
Wha?!
Oh. That's just a video
I had Ken make for me.
I thought it would help me
get your timing.
That's exactly why I came here.
I need to observe the way
you move in day-to-day life.
By living in close quarters,
I hope we can understand
each other's movements better.
So we understand each other's
movements better? Right.
She looks so elegant...
Oh my.
What's that?
Oh, nothing, I just thought
it looked cool how you took
your jacket off just then...
Mercy!
I was just about to go
get some dinner
in the dining hall, Layla.
Want me to bring you something?
No, I'll come eat with you.
Sora!
Wanna get some food?
What the--
What's she doing here?
Oh, she's going to be living
in my room for a little bit.
Huh?
Let's eat.
If they wanted
a new face for a costar,
they should've chosen one of us.
That fight would be perfect
if I'd done the show.
Could you keep
the line moving please?
I'm not finished
making my salad yet.
Layla's got a
really graceful walk.
Even when she's not
in front of an audience...
Do you want me
to make some coffee?
No thank you. But I would
like to use your shower.
Oh the nerve of her!
Are you sure?
Is something wrong?
Um, I uh--
No, of course not, silly!
Go ahead, take your time.
This is an outrage!
I'm a free spirit. I can't
be caged up like this!
Even the way she said
no to coffee was...
Look at that!
Ooh...
Uh, Layla,
wouldn't you be more comfortable
in a pair of my pajamas?
What's that?
You know, so you can get
in touch with my rhythms.
But how would that...?
Here, I'm pretty sure
this one would fit you.
But I don't--
Look, if you're gonna
stay in my room, you've got
to follow my rules, okay?
Whatever you say.
Oh, no, Layla, I want
you to take the bed.
I'm happy to sleep on the floor.
I'm sleeping on the floor
and that's final.
Sure.
Having Layla live with me,
having her sleep in my room...
If I can't get the timing
right after this-- No.
Don't think about that. I'll
get her rhythm down, I have to.
She looks like
a sleeping angel.
Hey! How did you get out?
Let's just say I was
exceptionally motivated.
The Tower. It means you
should expect the unexpected.
You mean like having Layla
come over for a surprise visit?
Huh. I'm good, aren't I?
Whatever. Just try not
to wake her up, okay?
Layla's movements.
Layla's pauses.
Layla's inner rhythms.
I've got to learn it.
I don't have a minute to lose!
They're spending all their
time together and they still
can't get in synch.
Late!
I'm sorry--
That's interesting.
I think those two are finally
getting on the same wavelength.
Sora's really been
giving it her all.
They're finally
starting to work together.
Their early scenes
are starting to fly.
But will all that momentum stall
once they get to the climax?
Jump!
I was too close!
Sure, I think
we can open on time.
However, I think we
should tone down the climax,
or else this whole show's
gonna blow up in our faces.
So you're saying you want
to make the fight scene easy?
Yes. For the time being, I think
we should cut the diabolo.
It just keeps
getting in the way.
What--
Breaking in a newcomer
is enough of a risk.
I don't want anyone
to get hurt up there.
As the director, I think this
is our only option right now.
But I can do it.
I've worked so hard--
I know you have, Sora.
But we're running out of time.
Unacceptable.
But, Layla, I'm only--
We can't hold back
on the climax.
The show'll fall apart.
All we need is one more day.
But tomorrow's the final dress!
We can't move that.
Are you saying we
postpone opening night?
We'll use stand-ins
for the final dress.
Are you serious?
Afraid so.
You won't be sorry, Kalos.
Sora?
Hey, Ken.
Where's Layla?
She said she needed to go
and make a couple phone calls.
So... What did they say?
Oh, well Layla kind of convinced
them to give us one more day.
Really? That's great!
I know, isn't it? See ya...
Oh, right. You're gonna
be awesome out there, Sora!
Thanks!
Good morning. Is it ready?
It's good to see you
this morning, Miss Hamilton.
Everything should be in order.
I appreciate it.
What is...
Hurry and get on the boat, Sora.
Coming!
And it looks like the weather's
going to cooperate, too.
I think you're right.
Those clouds
don't look good at all.
Excuse me, but ...
We're going to
practice out here.
What?
Uh Layla I know our timing
was starting to get much more
synchronized but is it safe
to do this over the water?
I want you to forget everything
you've learned up to this point.
Huh?
We've been beating our heads
against this routine,
trying to make every single move
perfect, but then I realized
having the fight be
perfect isn't enough.
It's the same kind of
safe choice I've been making
on stage for years.
What are you saying?
This has to be a real fight
between the two of us.
A real fight?
Between me and Layla?
So, what?
Will you do it or not?
Yes.
You can use a
lifeline if you want.
I'm not using one because it'll
just get in the way when I move.
Then I won't use one, either.
Fine.
You're starting to look
like you could be
a real adversary...
She's really serious about
this. If I drop my guard
for one second, she's gonna
toss me into the ocean!
Make that mistake again
and you're gonna be shark bait.
Out on the ocean,
she can't predict
when the next wave's gonna
come. So out here, Layla's...
Mm-hm. You heard me right.
They're in the middle of
a special rehearsal. I suggest
you have the final dress
without them.
I assure you, the show will open
tomorrow as scheduled. Yes.
No, Sarah,
it's not time for you yet.
I'm so sorry! I can't
believe I did that again...
That's nice. Make sure
you stay evenly spaced, folks!
Rick? Right about now
you need to make your way
to the front for your ad-lib.
Okay!
They're doing what?
But we're opening tomorrow--
what if they get hurt out there?
Layla would never do anything
to jeopardize a production.
But I am worried
about the weather.
They're like machines...
Are you ready to give up yet?
No way.
Oh, really?
Stop freaking out!
We just need you
to stay up there
'til we get the lights set.
Okay.
I don't know what
Kalos is thinking;
there's no way we
can open tomorrow...
No, Miss Hamilton!
You still in one piece?
Yeah!
I radioed the docks, and the
storm's even worse out there.
We'll be better off staying
out here until morning.
If you think it's best, okay.
Tomorrow we're doing
the show for real, huh?
Doing it for real...
What?
I wonder if Jean could
add some rain to the effects.
You know, you're
really incredible, Layla.
You're always thinking
of ways to make
Kaleido Stage shows better.
Do you mind if I ask why
you joined Kaleido Stage
in the first place?
When I was a little girl
I came to see one of
their shows with my parents.
It was wonderful, of course,
like a beautiful dream.
But the thing I liked
best about it was that
for the first time in my
life I could see my parents
laughing like children.
Really? Which show
did they take you to?
The show was
'Alice in Wonderland.'
'Alice in Wonderland?'
That's the one I saw with
my parents before they died.
It's one of my
favorite memories.
Because, seeing that
production was the last thing
my parents and I
ever did together.
It was the same way for me.
My mother had been sick.
That day was the first time
I ever heard her laugh so loud.
Unfortunately,
it was also the last time.
After she died,
my father tried to forget by
throwing himself into his work.
Wouldn't it be nice
if your father could see you
perform in this show?
I'm sorry, did I say
something I shouldn't have?
No.
I've never told anyone
about my family before.
It's almost like
she's got the power
to change people's hearts...
I think that one of these days
audiences are gonna flock here
just to see what she's up to.
We should try to get some rest.
Okay.
Oh, by the way, Sora,
are you aware that
you talk in your sleep?
Huh? No, I didn't know.
I wonder if she just heard me
talking to the Fool at night...
What's this?!
Looks like both of them
decided to spend the night
someplace else tonight.
How could they?!
Why wasn't I informed?!
Maybe they just got
held up somewhere...
Yes. That must be it.
I have no choice.
I'm staying put.
But, please, make sure
you're back by tomorrow night...
Kalos here. Hm.
I see. All right.
It's Kalos. We're going on
with opening night as planned.
Layla and Sora are on their way
to the theatre as we speak.
They should be arriving
any minute now!
Let's move.
So they've heard from Sora?
I'm glad. Looks like
they'll make it just in time!
It's them!
Sora!
Welcome back!
Jean, could you make it rain
during the fight scene?
Rain? Well, I could try...
I need my crew!
Welcome back!
It's good to be here!
She's faster than
she was yesterday.
Sweet...
All right, stand by
for flame ignition.
Okay, go.
Ignite them now.
Go on the flames.
Sora!
Thank you, Layla.
It's been a really long time
since I've heard the
audience applaud like this.
I'm so happy.
I don't know what to say.
I don't want this moment
to ever end!
This isn't so easy that
you'll get a standing ovation
for just following the script.
And so I've gotta keep working
hard. Even on my days off!
Sora's been asked
to be a guest performer
at another circus company.
And I'm going to look
after her while she's there.
And just when I'd gotten used
to how things worked
at Kaleido Stage...
I feel like I'm jumping out of
the frying pan into the fire!
Ouch!
Next time on Kaleido Star:
'Mysterious Amazing Circus.'
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...