Hey-there, everyone,
Kaleido Star is about to start,
so make sure that
your room is brightly lit
and that you're not sitting
too close to the TV, okay.
Well, well, well.
Everyone, it's Marion.
Say, I'd like to know,
do you love your mom?
My mom's not around anymore.
She died in an accident
when I was little.
She was very good at
doing the trampoline.
In fact, she was a star
at Kaleido Stage!
She was sweet and
very beautiful.
Oh, she was the best.
Even now, I still
love her very much.
And you know what?
I want to become a great woman
like my mom when I grow up, too!
Keep going after
my dream, she said.
So I guess Layla knows.
She knows that I've
lost sight of my dream.
It's kind of fitting
she gave me that advice.
Layla was the one who
inspired me to join
Kaleido Stage in
the first place.
And when my only
dream in the world
was to become a
Kaleido Star like her,
all I had to do was chase
after Layla with all my might.
And for me to do that,
I was willing to do
just about anything,
no matter how hard it was.
But now, I don't
know what to do.
I don't have a dream anymore.
Sora!
Have you seen my dad?
Oh, wow! You're adorable.
Look at you all dressed up.
What's the big event, Marion?
Today, I'm going to see my mom.
"Marion's Amazing Debut."
Here are your favorite
flowers, Casablanca lilies.
Aren't they pretty?
I bought them for you
in a flower shop
at the corner of North and Main.
But the clerk in the store
there has a real attitude,
and she's always treating
me like I'm a little child.
Boy, she made me
so mad the other day.
So, I told her "Why don't
you at least be nice to me,
since I'm a paying customer?"
And then she--
Hey, hey!
Marion, if you try to tell
her everything all at once,
you're going to make Mom dizzy.
Oh, right. I'm sorry, Mom.
Jonathan, wait up!
It's been six years, Cynthia.
But it still feels
like you died yesterday.
So much has happened
in the meantime.
Marion is now 10 years old.
Jonathan!
Don't you think she's turned
out to be a beautiful girl?
Grand Screw Jump!
Oh, dear. What's the matter?
He's scary!
Dracula's scary!
Don't worry. It's just a play.
No! He's scary!
Hi, there. Are you okay?
Thank you for coming today.
The children are scared?
Mm-hmm.
Leon's Dracula is realistic
and that has made the show
popular with the audience,
but it seems that small children
are being really scared by it.
It's too bad they're
not enjoying the show.
Poor kids.
Then, I have no choice...
I won't be your partner.
If only Kaleido Stage
could be the kind of place
where children
can enjoy the show
every bit as much
as the adults do.
The stage where everyone
can enjoy themselves...
I get it now...
A stage for the kids...
That's it!
Sora...?
Let's do it!
I'm going to assemble a
temporary stage around the pool.
Thanks, that'll be a big help.
It'll be ready for
practice tomorrow.
Is this show going
to be for kids?
Yeah, it is.
Saturdays, Sundays,
and between the matinee
and night shows of Dracula.
And it was Sora's bright idea.
We're going to show
everyone just how much fun
Kaleido Stage really is.
We got the Boss'
permission, too.
We just need a cast.
A "Kids' Stage"?
Between the regular
performances?
That's right.
It'll add to our work,
but if we take turns
playing the parts,
I think we can pull it off.
C'est stupid.
Don't do it.
Why do you say that?
The current shows are
increasing our audience.
We do not need one more.
The children in our
audience should be able to
enjoy Kaleido Stage every
bit as much as the adults.
That's the reason we need
something like Kids' Stage.
Instead of worrying
about something like that,
get the skills good
enough to satisfy me.
I agree it's important
for me to improve,
but I think Kids' Stage
is equally important.
You disobey me?!
I'm not gonna
give up Kids' Stage.
I can't believe this. She's
making me lose my composure.
You're a fool.
--Oh no.
--What are we gonna do?
May!
Thanks, but I would
rather concentrate
on the role I play now.
Besides, if I'm to be a
suitable partner for Leon,
I'll need to spend time
in special training
to improve my skills.
That's what I'll be doing
while you play with the kids.
--Sorry Sora.
--No way.
--I can't do this.
--Sorry.
Sorry Sora.
I thought everyone would be
eager to help out
with the Kids' Stage.
Sora, you can do this show
even with a small crew.
And you can count on
me to help you out.
Sarah!
Me, too.
Rosetta!
It's been a while since
I've had the chance
to perform in front of kids.
If you want,
we could do the trapeze.
Sorry, the show
doesn't have trapeze.
Oh, really? Well then,
I'll do diabolo.
A mortal blow!
Young Chick Style!
--Peep, peep...
--Excuse me...
If you don't mind...
I'd like for you to sing or...
--Peep!
--Any song, any song at all...
I want to educate the audience
about the world's
unknown martial arts.
--Uh, a song, please...
--PEEP!
You're amazing, Rosetta.
Finish it after that move.
Looks good.
Hey, Mia...
No gags, please.
How about if I fall on my face,
or something like that?
Uh, No.
Okay. Here I go!
Jonathan, get ready!
Here I go!
I'm really doing it this time!
He's doing his
best to ignore her.
Jonathan, give me
back that ball.
Jonathan! I'm waiting!
She doesn't notice.
Jonathan!
You're awful.
Marion!
--Give me those.
--Sure.
Here goes, Jonathan!
Here! Here! Here!
There you go Jonathan,
you got it!
Marion's amazing!
Their timing's perfect.
You can see they spend
all their time together.
So Sora just wasn't good enough
to be Jonathan's partner, huh!
On days when I don't have to
attend director's meetings,
I can take turns
juggling with Sora.
Then why don't you ask
Marion to take your place?
Oh, that's an excellent idea.
That's right!
If someone the same age
as the kids is on stage,
I'm sure they'll end up
enjoying the show more.
I'm gonna do it. I will.
It's decided. Sora,
you switch to trampoline.
I'll do my best.
Jonathan is a really
quick learner, Dad.
He picked up using
a ball just like that,
and now he's learned how to
turn a ring with his nose.
Really?
But if we end up having a big
audience, he may get nervous.
Oh, but don't have
to worry about me.
I've always been fairly
strong under pressure.
So you're happy about
being on stage, huh, Marion?
That's not how it is at all.
Jonathan says that
the only person
who can be his partner is me.
I have to do it.
I see...
Here I go, Jonathan!
Here!
Here! Here!
Ah!
You'll pay for this!
Jonathan, wait!
Okay, I'm coming for you!
Well, do you give up now?
I'm so happy we're going
to be my partners, Sora.
Pa-Partners? Well...
Marion's on the trampoline...
A few years ago,
her mother was the star
of our trampoline act.
So she really knows a lot
about performing on it.
And people thought
she would follow
in her mother's footsteps and
become a Kaleido Star, too.
But after her mother died,
she just quit the trampoline.
Marion!
This is the first time I've
seen you on the trampoline,
and you were amazing!
Like mother, like daughter.
What do you mean?
I was just playing around.
Please don't tell my dad.
OK we'll practice
it again, Jonathan.
Right after school.
Marion was doing the trampoline?
Yes.
Her performance is
so free and beautiful.
If she keeps practicing at it,
I bet she'll get even better.
It shouldn't be surprising.
Marion's mother was
a top trampoline star,
and Marion must have learnt it
by watching what her
mother did in practice.
Why, people used to
say all the time,
"Those two will be mother and
daughter Kaleido Stars"...
Oh, wow...
I wonder why she
quit the trampoline.
Maybe it's because the
trampoline reminds her
of her mom and
that makes her sad.
She may be afraid of
getting hurt while jumping.
Yeah, maybe...
But when I saw her jumping,
Marion looked like
she was having fun.
That's what I thought, too.
And why did she ask us
not to tell her dad?
So she wants to keep it
a secret from Jean?
Marion!
Why did you tell my dad?
Why did you tell him? I asked
you not to tell my dad, Sora.
Marion, did you jump
on the trampoline today?
Huh?
Now tell me the truth, Marion...
No, I didn't.
No, I didn't jump!
Jean knew?
Is it possible he overheard
our conversation?
Sorry...
I don't ever want to see my Dad
with that look
on his face again.
What?
I can't stand to see
my Dad look so sad!
And if I were to get hurt
doing the trampoline,
I'm sure it would
break his heart.
That's the reason why I don't
do the trampoline anymore.
I gave it up for my Dad.
So that's why.
Marion, I'm sorry for not
understanding how you feel.
Still, though...
I'm gonna do it. I will.
I mean... are you really sure?
Because I thought you wanted to
grow up to be like your mom.
Why do you say
things like that?!
Oh, Marion!
What's with her?
It's almost time for places.
Marion really loves
the trampoline,
but she's afraid
of hurting her Dad.
I wonder if there's anything
I can do to help her out.
Sagittarius is sinking
further and further
into the darkness
of uncertainty.
The key to getting
out of the darkness
is to be found
in Aquarius' girl.
Hey, Marion.
About this afternoon...
If you're talking about me doing
the trampoline, don't worry.
I have no interest
at all in doing it.
Um, Marion, do you remember
the shows Mom used to do?
She was so pretty.
She looked like a bird
flying free in the sky.
I especially loved the
way your Mom went about
performing on the trampoline.
Daddy...
I have something I've been
wanting to show you, Marion.
Huh?
Hmm?
Here, take a look at this.
What's this?
Daddy... this is...
Your mom's stage notebook.
I'm sorry for
hiding it from you.
I thought seeing it
would make you sad.
This was Mom's.
Your Mom was always trying
to come up with new acts,
and she would jot down
her ideas in this notebook.
Then she would practice
them over and over again
until she could
do them perfectly.
"Marion's Debut Stage"...
That's right.
Your mom would come up with
all of the performance ideas,
and then I would come up
with all of stage ideas.
I remember we talked
about it daily,
and every once in a while,
we'd even argue.
Your mom wanted to
appear on the stage
and do the trampoline
with you one day.
That was your mom's dream.
Mama... that's also my dream...
I've always wanted to appear
on the stage with you,
and together,
do the trampoline...
Marion...
Marion, when I found out
you were practicing your
routines on the trampoline,
I was really happy.
And you know what,
I'm pretty sure your Mom would
feel the same way as I do.
Would she really?
Yeah.
You like the trampoline,
don't you Marion?
Then for your mom's sake,
I want you to become
even better at it.
Really?
Wow, this is amazing.
Yeah, it looks fun.
It's also the perfect kind
of act for the Kids' Stage!
Then why don't we
add it in the show?
Yeah, I think that's a really
good idea. Way to go, Marion.
If I might ask,
what are we going to do
about Cynthia's role?
Oh... I don't know...
Sora, will you do it for me?
Yeah!
--Are you sure?
--You don't want to?
No, That's not it.
It was your mom's role.
Yep. I want you to do it.
In that case, my answer is yes!
Yaay!
Wow, things are
getting exciting!
Does this mean I'm going
to be Jonathan's partner?
Hey, that's not a bad idea.
Jonathan, let's do our best.
They laughed...
Okay, Jonathan,
say hello to everyone!
Ready? Go!
That looks good on you, Marion.
This is the place
where my mom was.
Ready? Jump!
Oh...
Jump!
Why is it, when people
perform with Sora,
they always end up smiling?
Marion.
They went against my expressed
wishes to create this?
How frivolous.
Wait, Leon.
Look, everyone is smiling!
This is the real Kaleido Stage.
Maybe this is the Kaleido
Stage I'm aiming for.
Maybe! Maybe!
I can see why they call
him the lord of darkness.
So this is the circus festival
that's held once
every three years!
Miss Layla won the last festival
by doing the Golden Phoenix.
My partner is Leon,
lord of darkness.
Then, tragedy strikes May.
Just watch, I will
definitely be a contestant!
I will! I will!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Amazing Training With Leon."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...