Hey, everyone, we're
gonna watch Kaleido Star,
so make sure your room is
brightly lit and that you're
not sitting too close to the TV.
Well, well, well.
Do any of you have siblings?
Older brothers or sisters
who take care of you,
or little brothers and
sisters that you take care of?
In my family it's always
been just me and my parents,
but soon there's
going to be a new baby.
I should be really happy, but
part of me is kinda nervous.
What do I do, what do I do?
I know. But you
don't need to worry.
I'm going to get an apartment
with some of my friends.
And we've decided to make
our own theatre company!
Well, yes, I know it'll be
hard, but we've gotta try.
So I guess I won't be visiting
you for a little while.
Oh, wow that's really... I
guess what I'm supposed to say
is congratulations.
That's great news, Mom.
I'm really happy for you!
I what? I sound weird to you?
No, no, nothing's wrong...
'Amazing Family Ties.'
All right, as of today
I'm starting a new life.
A new life... I should
be happy for them.
Why am I being so selfish?
No need to look so glum, Sora.
I am coming with you after all.
You're gonna live with us?
That's so sweet. You were
afraid you might lose me.
If I catch you peeping at Mia
or Anna I'm feeding you
to Jonathan, you hear me?
Uh right.
Thanks for waiting!
Come on, you're late.
Are you finally ready to go?
Yes.
Then let's get out of here.
Your family's great
to take us in until
we find can find a place.
They've really been looking
forward to meeting you guys,
especially --
Hi, Sarah.
You're all packed up
and ready to go I see.
Where are you going?
Right now? To training.
See you later...
To training?
You think she meant
for her singing?
Knowing her, I think it's
probably for martial arts.
Yeah, that sounds
more like Sarah's style.
Seriously, Ken, your
family's a lifesaver.
My grandmother would've
made me come home if I
didn't have a place to stay.
Yeah, I was gonna wait
to tell my Mom about this,
but Yuri's buy-out is
already all over the news.
Well, there was no way I was
going to stand by and let
the three of you be homeless.
Wow you sound so manly, Ken.
Stop making fun of me.
Sorry...
Sora?
Is something bothering you?
No, I'm fine, really.
Sora!
Your suitcase!
Hey!
Just one more thing:
before you meet my family,
there's something
I need to tell you...
What is it?
Now, I've already
talked to her about it,
but my younger sister might...
This is it.
Wow, this is like a little park!
Yeah my father built
all of this himself.
He built this? That's amazing!
Yeah, I know, but about
my little sister..
Anna! I can't believe it's you!
This is for you!
Now pose with it!
Come on, pose!
This is my little sister,
Lucy. She's Anna's biggest fan.
You're kidding, right?
Ken!
It's rude to keep our guests
outside. Please. Come in, girls.
This way, Anna.
Uh, this is my Mom-- oh, boy...
Ben! Wake up.
Our guests are here.
It's nice to meet you!
Oh, uh, thank you.
Really, napping in
the middle of the day...
I wasn't napping, I was
thinking of design ideas.
I've heard that before.
Now, welcome our guests, Ben.
My father's a designer--
of furniture mostly.
Oh.
Don't be shy, girls,
come on in and have a seat.
Does everyone like coffee?
Yeah, that sounds great.
Hey Anna. Come on, sit down.
Make yourself at home.
Wow! I can't believe
Anna's sitting on our couch!
Somehow... Anna's different
than I expected...
Sorry about that.
You don't like it?
Well not really.
You're right, posing like a
monkey is such a tired cliché.
Oooh!
Yeah! That's great!
...And this is the last one.
The three of you will
be staying in here.
Right. Thank you.
Awesome!
Glad you like it. This
used to be the playroom,
so sorry if it's
a little childish.
No. It's wonderful!
Did you design all the
furniture in here, too?
Yep, and if you find anything
you like, I want you to take it
with you when you move
into your own apartment.
You mean it?!
Here. It's something
new to pose with.
Put me down! Put me down! I
wanna stay with Anna! Daddy!
So I, uh, guess I'll
see you guys at dinner.
Anna! Daddy!
We have got
to find our own place.
And quick.
This used to be the play room.
Once my mother and father's
real child is born,
I wonder if I...
Sora, are you all right?
You've been really
quiet all day today.
No I haven't!
How'd he get in there?
Sora?
He's gone.
Where is he?
What are you talking about?
Is it a bug or something?
Sora?
What the heck are you doing?
Gotcha!
I'm sorry. I made that noise.
Do you think I can make up for
by helping you prepare dinner.
We'd like to help, too.
Well, thank you, girls. And
don't you worry about the noise.
It was getting too
quiet around here.
Ken used to jump off of
that top bunk all the time
when he was a boy.
Really?
Yes. He always dreamed of
being a star at Kaleido Stage.
It's really too bad
he had such a weak heart.
His condition doesn't prevent
him from living a normal life,
but I'm afraid becoming
an acrobat was simply
out of the question.
It was hard for
him to give it up.
He fought against it
for a long time.
But, as his mother,
I'm glad he's done with it.
I'm always afraid he's going
to come home one day and say
he's started performing again.
Ken! Give me my camera back!
No way. You've already pestered
Anna enough with it today.
I need pictures or my friends
won't believe she's here!
Why don't you just
invite them over, then?
So they can see for themselves.
Good idea!
Dad, will you please
stop encouraging her?
Oh how funny my little brother
and I used to fight like
that all the time, as well.
Sometimes I used to argue
with my mother like that.
At home I don't
think we ever fought.
Hey, who's hungry?!
Sora?
Ken?
Can't sleep, huh?
No, it's just
so nice out here...
Sorry my family's so noisy.
Oh, no, I think
it's kinda nice.
I mean, how all of you can say
exactly what's on your mind,
just like a real family.
What are you
trying to say, Sora?
That your parents don't
feel like real family?
Oh, of course not. I didn't
mean it the way it sounded.
Do you mind if I ask you
what you've been so
worried about today?
I'm not worried. Actually,
I just heard some good news.
My mother's going
to have a baby!
So you're gonna be
a sister. You excited?
They always wanted kids.
I used to wonder if they'd never
had their own because of me.
That they didn't want to
make me feel like an outsider.
Silly, huh?
Sometimes it's not
easy having a sibling.
It was rough
when Lucy was born.
Seemed like my parents spent
so much time caring for her
that they didn't
notice me anymore.
I used to be bad on purpose
just so my mom and dad
would pay attention to me.
I'm too old to do something
like that. I've never even
argued with them,
I don't want to start now.
Besides, I'd be afraid of...
breaking our family bond...
I don't think that's possible.
Well, don't be afraid of arguing
with me. I mean maybe you and I
can be the kind of
family you want.
You're right, Ken.
We are kind of like family.
Sora...
You, me, Mia and Anna.
Because the four of us
are going to make our
very own Kaleido Stage.
There's no time
to sit around moping.
First thing tomorrow morning
we're gonna find an apartment.
Good night, Ken!
But that isn't
what I meant at all.
That's right. I've got a family
here that I can turn to.
And we're gonna make
a theatre company my parents
will be proud to see!
Don't ever stop
being my friends.
That Sora...
She should be ashamed
of the way she treats me...
The Empress?!
See you later!
Are you all right?
Mm-hm.
Wow, this one has
it's very own front yard!
Too much.
A rental house in the
suburbs might be a good idea.
Too far.
How about this?
It's not as expensive
and it's closer to town.
No way.
Oh, hi.
What's wrong with living here?
Well, this building gets
broken into every other day.
Oh...
We're never gonna find
an apartment, are we?
Huh... Maybe I can help you...
Well, this is it.
You're kidding.
Aw, c'mon, it's not as bad as it
looks. It's in a great location,
the rent is cheap and --
You'd have an excellent
downstairs neighbor.
Doctor Kate?!
This is it.
Wow...
So?
It's just what
we're looking for.
Told ya.
It's a lot cleaner than
it looks from the outside.
And it's so big!
What a great view.
Yeah. It's perfect.
Right.
You know, I think
I'd like living here.
Me too.
Then it's settled.
From here we're going to
start our own Kaleido Stage.
Nothing can get in our way!
And I live right downstairs,
so just let me know if you girls
need anything at all, okay?
It's perfect, isn't it?
Well, come on.
Let's go to my place and
I'll make you some coffee.
We're going to your apartment?
You can move something if you
want to sit on the chairs.
She's totally hot
but she lives in filth.
Maybe it isn't so perfect.
We're gonna have to come down
here and clean this place
if we don't want
a bug infestation.
But that's a small price to
pay for such a great place.
Jerry, what have you
done with the coffee?
Jerry?
I didn't know his name
was Jerry, did you?
It's cute!
You know it suits him.
Watch it! You'd better
not make fun of my name!
Who'd have thought
we'd find a place so soon?
I know, we're lucky!
But Lucy's gonna
be so disappointed
that we're moving out.
Maybe we should
leave Anna there?
Not funny.
Who's Ken talking
to over there?
Oh, Sora!
Sora.
It's my Mom and my Dad.
Thank you very much.
Oh, sure.
That was a really long trip
for Mrs. Naegino to make.
I wonder if they want
to take Sora back home.
And right when we
finally found an apartment...
You should've let me
know you were coming.
I would've come to meet you.
We decided to come
at the last minute.
We went to the dormitory--
they said you'd been kicked out.
Oh, sorry. I was going to call
you once we found an apartment.
Is it okay for you to travel,
I mean since it's so
close to your due date?
I'm perfectly fine.
Your mother insisted on
coming here to check on you.
Because you sounded just
terrible over the phone.
Did I sound that bad?
I'm so sorry.
But you don't have anything
to worry about, 'cause I'm fine.
I can't tell how
you're doing over the phone.
Oh really? Um I'm good--
we found a new apartment.
My friend the policeman,
you met him, Dad, you remember,
he showed us the place.
Isn't that great?
And his friend Kate
lives downstairs from us,
she's a doctor.
I think he's secretly
in love with her, too,
but he says there's
nothing going--
Sora. I want you
to come back Japan with us.
Now that you're not
with Kaleido Stage,
I don't know how you're
going to make a living here.
Well, you see, my friends
and I are going to--
I know, you want to create
your own Kaleido Stage.
But why can't you
do that in Japan?
You wouldn't have to work,
so you'd be free to
come up with new ideas.
And your father and I wouldn't
have to worry about whether
you were getting
enough to eat. We--
Once you have your own child
you won't have time
to worry about me anymore.
I'm not going to matter to you.
Sora...
You're being ridiculous!
How could we ever forget about
you? You are our child, Sora.
I didn't mean...
This isn't how
I wanted this to happen.
I'm sorry, Sora. I just--
Midori?
Mom?!
Oh my goodness. Ken,
call an ambulance, quickly.
Right.
Ben! Get the car ready!
Midori! Hold on!
Please lay down. The
ambulance will be here soon.
Midori? Midori!
Mom!
A Cesarian section? But she's
only in her seventh month.
This is an emergency. You
have no choice, Mr. Naegino.
Ben, please. Stop pacing,
you're making me nervous.
Right.
What have I done?
Sora, don't worry. Your mother
is going to be all right.
I said such a terrible thing
to her, Ken. And now she...
Sora this isn't your fault.
No. I've been so dumb.
I just thought that once she
has a baby once she has a baby
of her own she
won't need me anymore.
So even though I know
she's so excited about this,
I haven't I haven't been able
to be really happy for her.
I hated myself for feeling
this way, and I knew that if
I went back to Japan
she'd see how selfish I am.
That's why I I said
all those things.
She was trying so hard
to be a good mother to me
and I pushed her away.
And now now she might lose
the baby because of me.
Sora. A truly selfish person
could never be this worried
about someone else.
You don't want anything bad
to happen to her or the baby.
That's what being
a family's about.
Nothing you say could
ever destroy that.
You'll be there for
each other, no matter what.
Your mother and the baby
are working hard in there.
Let's cheer them on.
You're right. Thank you, Ken.
Oh, Mom, please be all right.
And the baby...
Please, please let it be born
safely. That's all I want.
They're both okay.
And it's a girl.
Your mother's taking
a rest right now.
She's had a long evening.
Thank you for everything.
She's so tiny.
Well, she was
two months premature.
She's all right, Sora.
This is just like
when you were born.
You were premature and had to
be kept in an incubator, too.
I remember your mother
and father were
so worried about you.
They blamed themselves,
too and they hated not
being able to hold you.
Every time they'd
come to visit you,
they'd tell you to grow up
strong and healthy.
I remember it like
it was yesterday,
the two of them cheering you on.
They couldn't wait
to take you home.
When you told me you
wanted to join Kaleido Stage,
the first thing I thought was,
'What would her father say?'
And I guess I'll never
know what he would've done.
But I think they would have
let you go just like we did.
And they would've been just as
worried about their little Sora,
even though their little
Sora's all grown up and able
to take care of herself.
But I guess that's just
what mothers and fathers do,
don't they.
They never stop worrying
about their children.
Just like Midori and I can't
stop worrying about you, huh?
Thanks, Dad.
Sora. Why don't you go
visit your mother now?
Sora. I gave you
all a scare, didn't I?
Mom, I-- I'm so sorry.
For what? Sora, nothing that
happened today was your fault.
But, Mom. I said those terrible
things to you. And then this.
The worst part is
I knew I hurt you.
I knew you couldn't leave
and I said something that
drove you into a corner.
I was being
really unfair to you.
So you said something you didn't
want to say. I pushed you.
No.
I'm sorry. To tell the truth,
your father and I came here
because I wanted you
to be at home with me...
I wanted you to be there
when the baby was born.
After all, you're the
only older sister she's got,
and when you told me on the
phone you weren't coming home
Well, I lost my composure
and I made your father get us
on the next flight to Cape Mary.
But I guess
I got my wish anyway.
You were here for
your sister's birth.
I'm so glad.
Will you come
closer to me, Sora?
Sure.
I'm so proud of
the way you've grown up.
When we adopted you, I was
afraid Chikara and I would never
be able to fill your parents'
place in your heart.
I think you were worried about
that, too. I still remember
the first time you ever
called me 'Mother.'
I was so happy I felt
like crying for a week.
Even though you're all grown up
you're still our little girl.
We'll always worry about you,
but when we know that you're
doing well, we're happy.
We love you very much, Sora.
Oh, Mom.
If you ever need anything
don't be afraid to ask.
And Sora?
Yes?
I'd like you
to name your sister.
Are you sure you want me to--
I've always wanted you
to name my baby.
Oh...
Mom just called,
they're both all right!
That's great!
I'm so glad!
Come on, let's celebrate!
Call everyone!
Everyone?
Who else needs to know?
The Empress card is also known
to foretell childbirth...
She's lovely.
She really is. Congratulations.
Thanks.
We are so grateful for
everything you've done.
Oh. Well, we didn't do
anything extraordinary...
You should both be
very proud of your son.
Proud of me? Oh, wow!
You're here, little sister.
You've made our dreams
come true. And from now on,
I'm going to do my best
to achieve my dreams, too.
That's it!
What?
I thought of a name for her!
Yume! What do you think?
It's perfect.
That means 'dream,' right, Dad?
Did you say Dad?
Uh, I mean...
Yume... I can't wait
to see you grow up!
I want to do something
to repay Sora's kindness.
So we're doing our own show,
and it's full of
exciting new challenges.
And even though Layla
rejected our invitation...
...Rosetta came to help us
put together a new company.
And a mysterious masked
performer keeps showing up
from out of nowhere.
But who is she? Who? Who? Who?
Join us next time for 'Amazing
Change from Zero to Hero.'
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...