Hey everyone, Kaleido
Star's about to start,
so make sure that
your room is brightly lit,
and that you're not
sitting too close to the TV.
There are challengers,
adventurers, and pioneers,
those people whom
we commonly label 'fools.'
Wise people follow those fools.
They praise those who succeed
and laugh at those who fail.
Such is the way of the world.
But a true star will never
stop trying to be her best.
No mockery can stop her.
A fool aims for goals
no one has yet reached.
She aims to be a Kaleido Star
like no one has ever seen.
Sora Naegino,
I don't accept that you're
the next Kaleido Star.
No, I don't.
"An Amazing New Rival."
He's just so wonderful.
Those mysterious eyes of his
are just so irresistible.
Mr. Leon!
I'll get to see him any second.
Mom, will Sora be in the show?
Will she have a big part?
Yes.
Where's Sora?
Is she here yet, Mia?
No, not yet.
Ken, she's not in the
lobby or the dressing room!
I wonder where she went.
That Sora is
a very naughty girl.
I don't get it Miss Sarah,
why are you laughing?
I have a feeling that our little
Sora is doing something absurd.
Well I still don't
see why that's funny.
She's such a big star
now that maybe she thinks
she's allowed to be
late on opening day.
Marion, aren't you
supposed to be helping your
father right about now?
No, not really.
And to tell you the truth,
I just came to see Leon Oswald.
Oh, of course.
He is the prince
of the French circus,
the Pegasus of the stage.
The most talented performer
in the whole world!
But no one knows his past...
He's so mysterious.
There's no time
for this conversation.
This is the first day
she's going to appear
on stage with Mr. Oswald.
And she still doesn't believe
she can draw an
audience by herself.
Sora! Where could you be?
I found her.
Look!
What?
What is she doing?
With Layla gone, we've lost
some of our audience, so...
I think Sora's trying
to win them back by
advertising the show.
Uh, dang it!
I'm going too!
Please don't, Anna!
So I can't go?
Everybody!
Kaleido Stage is fun!
So come-
There.
She did it!
You're great!
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
I wonder if that helped
with the advertising.
You guys, please come see
Kaleido Stage, okay?
It's a wonderful show that
combines an interesting play
with some amazing
acrobatic elements.
I've seen something like that.
And Layla's not in it, is she?
Hey, could you do
that trick for us again?
Please.
But, I have to get
going, soon. Sorry.
You can do it.
Come on, do the trick.
Do the trick that you-
All right, I'll do it
just one more time.
Shoot, I'm gonna have to
hurry or I'll really be late.
Oh, I'll take a shortcut.
Please come see the
new show at Kaleido Stage.
Huh?
Please come see the
new show at Kaleido Stage.
The top performer in
the world, Leon Oswald,
will be appearing on
the stage starting today.
Saiyuki is a love story.
We can't start the
show without Sora,
she's playing the princess.
Everyone just concentrate
on getting ready.
Oh, here she comes.
Sora has arrived.
Everybody, get to places.
We're starting.
I'm sorry.
I lost track of time.
You're so late!
What were you thinking?
Oh, Boss, I was-I was just
thinking that Mr. Oswald came
all this way, so I thought I'd
do a little advertising for it.
You'd do well to keep your
mind on your work from now on.
But, I was thinking
about the show.
Even a trained seal
could get us publicity.
Huh?
Could you really?
I can understand why
he's upset with me,
but still, my name alone can't
draw the kind of audience
that Layla's could,
and that's why...
I'm sorry!
You're really hopeless.
Go change your clothes!
Okay!
Oh, Mr. Oswald, I'm really
sorry for being late.
I'm gonna do my best.
I look forward to sharing
the stage with you.
You don't need
to appear on stage.
But, I-
I can do the show myself.
He is so cool!
Except he shouldn't have said
something like that to you.
What are you gonna do?
I'll just go on stage
anyway, of course.
Doing the show all by himself.
I don't think he
was really serious.
I've gotta change.
Oh no, I can't reach.
You know, if you want,
I can help you get that off.
Thank you.
Fool?
I just need help taking off
this costume, and nothing else.
I know what you meant.
Okay, go ahead.
Right.
Darn.
You just said "darn" didn't you?
"Darn"?
I did not. Now stay still,
you don't have much time.
Darn.
You just said it again.
You did, you did, Fool!
Aren't you in a hurry?
I thought you'd go to heaven
or something, once we perfected
the legendary great maneuver.
I'm the spirit of the stage,
not some kind of ghost.
I made Mr. Oswald mad, but
he'll forgive me if he sees
I'm working really hard to make
this performance exciting,
don't you think?
Your sign is Sagittarius.
Those born under this sign head
straight for their dreams,
but you don't have
enough radiance yet.
You still have a long way
to go to become a star.
I'm putting all
my faith in you, Sora.
You want me to be
your dream, Layla?
I do, because I know
you have what it takes
to be a true Kaleido Star.
I am.
Don't be depressed.
If you can still see me, that
means that you still have-
I'm fine. Leave me alone!
I'll just have to do my best, no
matter what happens out there!
And that's all!
That's all! That's all!
Huh?
Oh yeah.
How cute!
Good, they like it!
It's one of my plans
working just fine.
Now on to phase two.
Why did I agree to this?
Hopefully Mr. Oswald
will think...huh?
He's not there.
What happened to him?
Where could he have gone to?
Hey wait a minute,
I can't believe this.
Is he really gonna leave?
What is going on?
Mr. Oswald!
Please, go back out on stage.
Change of plans.
Let's bring the
clowns out right now.
Hello!
I... oh, please don't go!
The show's not even over.
If we're just going to
show them amateurish stunts,
I'd rather not perform at all.
But that's not fair to all the
people who came to see the show.
The audience came
to see me at my best.
Doing a show in which
I don't shine is pointless.
But isn't the whole point
of doing a show like this
to entertain the audience
and make them happy?
We owe it to them
to at least finish.
You've got it backwards.
I did not come here
for the audiences.
The audiences came here for me.
I have the best technical
skills in the world.
The only reason the audience
came is to admire them.
If I knew Kaleido Stage
was a place that put on
stupid performances to curry
favor with the audience,
I never would have come
in the first place.
There are kids out there
who don't know anything
about you or your skills.
So what about them?
I'm not performing
for little kids.
Who would have guessed that
the one who perfected the
legendary great maneuver
would be this kind of person.
I should never have come here.
You know, you may have the best
technical skills in the world,
but that doesn't change the
fact that I don't like you.
But I understand that
Kaleido Stage needs you
out there right now.
Because my skills alone
can't draw the kind of audiences
that we used to get here.
So, please, I'm asking you to
go back on stage, Mr. Oswald.
No way.
The clowns' routine
is almost over.
What?
Oh no, what do we do?
We have no choice.
We'll have to cancel the show.
Is that okay, Boss?
All right.
You can't!
You can't cancel the show!
If he won't go back on stage,
I'll finish the
whole thing by myself.
What?
That's going to be interesting.
If I can finish the show by
myself, will you promise not to
leave Kaleido Stage?
I won't promise any such thing.
If you want to pull a
stunt like this, go ahead.
But you should learn that
the audience is a
performer's greatest enemy.
What do you mean the
audience is my enemy?
Finishing the show means you'll
have to do all of your maneuvers
and Leon's back-to-back
without a rest.
That's physically impossible.
And what are you going to
do in the last scene when
the two leads are
supposed to meet again?
Don't worry.
I know I can pull
this off somehow.
But Ken, I need
to ask you a favor.
That doesn't look
a thing like Leon.
What's going on?
I can do this.
I'm gonna pull this off,
no matter what!
Good! I can do it!
Layla entrusted
Kaleido Stage to me.
No matter what happens,
I've got to protect it!
In order to protect it,
we need Mr. Oswald.
No matter what kind
of person he is.
I'm not performing
for little kids.
Children are an important
part of our audience.
Just like when I was a
little girl and saw a show here
for the first time.
It was whimsical and fun.
I lost myself watching it.
That's what
Kaleido Stage is about.
Hurry!
Good luck.
Thanks.
What a quick change.
I can't show how tired I feel.
This has got to be
a lot. Even for her.
She must be reaching her limit.
I've never seen someone
as reckless as this one.
I've never seen anyone go
as far as she does, either.
Hmph.
But I think someone like that
has a good chance of becoming
a shining star, don't you?
Oh no.
It's time for
the big fight scene.
Do you think she can do it?
To land on top of the
mountain while spinning
is already difficult, but...
Since she's been staggering
so much, she's got no choice
but to slow down the spins.
But if she does that, the
maneuver will be incomplete.
She's speeding up.
Impossible!
She's so awkward I can
hardly stand to watch her.
Even so, I've never seen
anyone quite like her before.
Sora Naegino.
This last part is the reunion
scene with the princess.
Go!
Go for it!
From this point on, the show's
going to change depending on
Sora's ideas out there.
I'll be giving you instructions.
I hear you loud and clear.
Ken, are you ready?
Ready.
Okay, lights out.
That's good. Now bring up
spotlight number five.
Wow, it's the princess!
You're right!
There she is!
All right, it's working!
Pretty!
Lights down.
Now bring up B.
Awesome.
Bring on Leon Oswald.
This is terrible.
This is awful.
Where is Leon Oswald?
Leon! Leon!
Leon! Leon! Leon!
You should learn
that the audience is
a performer's greatest enemy.
The performance
went well, but...
This doesn't sound good.
How pitiful, Sora Naegino.
Uh, excuse me?
I heard that Leon Oswald
absolutely refused to be
your partner anymore.
Isn't that why you're
performing for two?
What do you want me to do?
Uh, well, well, I-
Oh, I don't care.
Let them continue.
You're the boss, sir.
What?
She's a trapeze artist, too?
Eternal Angel Turn!
She's using the swing
so freely and easily.
The Dreamer's Spiral!
Amazing. She's so bold, she
performs with such confidence.
You see now? I'm the one
who's good enough
to be Leon Oswald's partner.
You, on the other hand,
aren't fit to shine his shoes,
Sora Naegino.
Who's that?
She was the applicant
with the highest score
in our audition this year.
What's going on?
Is this part of the show?
Where's my Leon?
Excuse me, who are you?
Who am I?
I am the next Layla Hamilton,
that's who I am.
I'm gonna kick you out
and be the biggest star
this place has ever seen.
From now on, you can't call
yourself a star around here
if you don't
have any talent.
You got that?
Hey look, it's Leon!
If either of them
could be my partner,
it might be worth
sticking around.
If only for a little bit longer.
Mr. Oswald?
I changed my mind.
I've decided to stay
here a little bit longer.
You're staying?
Then you'll appear
on stage with me?
He isn't staying for you.
He's staying for me.
Leon Oswald is truly great, and
he can see how talented I am.
Both of you, follow me
in an improvisation.
Let's go.
Right.
Wonder...
Arrow!
Well, what's going on?
They're fighting.
If I remember right,
that's May Wong,
the girl who gave
the best audition.
But why?
Layla entrusted
Kaleido Stage to me.
I've got to protect it!
I've got the talent to fill
the shoes of a Kaleido Star,
not you!
A new kind of Kaleido Stage
has been set in motion.
I'm not a little kid anymore.
Rosetta came and said she wanted
to be a part of Kaleido Stage,
but it seems that there's
a reason behind this.
Sora, please help me.
You're the only
one I can turn to.
Of course, I want to do
what I can for Rosetta, but...
All right, for my
beloved friend Rosetta,
I'm gonna do my
very best to help.
I will! I will! I will!
Next time on Kaleido Star:
'The Amazing Newcomer.'
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky!