Hey, everyone, Kaleido Star
is about to start,
so make sure that
your room is brightly lit
and that you're not sitting
too close to the TV, all right?
Let's go!
Kaleido Stage.
It is a place where lighting
and sound can create
what seems to be magic.
To many, it is the best
theatre in the world,
the place that first captured
their hearts and let them dream.
Once upon a time, there was
a girl who aspired to be
part of this theatre...
Help! Help me!
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
I am so sorry!
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am the spirit of
the stage, The Fool.
I will be your guide today,
as I bring you up-to-date
on Sora Naegino's short
but remarkable career.
She came from Japan, aspiring
to be part of Kaleido Stage.
I'm finally here!
Sixteen year-old
Sora had arrived.
...and become a
big huge mega superstar!
I can, I shall, I will!
She came with such high hopes,
but a run of bad luck threatened
to shatter her dreams forever.
She used her strong will
and athletic abilities
to stop the thief.
Poor guy.
Finally, Sora arrived at
Kaleido Stage for her audition.
Oh, no, I can't
believe I'm so late.
Oh thank God I'm here.
Uh, and you are...?
Uh, my name is
Sora Naegino, sir.
I apologize for my tardiness.
Oh, I'm sorry Miss, but the
auditions have already ended.
Huh?
But I came all the way
from Japan just to be
in these auditions.
Huh? Well, perhaps we have
time for one more performer.
Oh, thank you so much.
You won't regret this, I-
No.
Oh, uh, Miss Layla.
The auditions are over.
Layla Hamilton, I can't
believe it's really her.
Uh, but wait,
there's a reason I'm late!
Don't you know that
a stage production
always starts on time?
But, I-
Go back home.
No, wait, you don't even
know what I can do, yet!
Miss Layla, please!
I absolutely, positively,
just really want
to join the Kaleido Stage!
Oh, please, Miss Layla.
I made a promise to my parents,
that if I failed today,
then I'd quit.
Sora could feel her
dreams slipping away.
If they wouldn't
see her audition,
she could never even hope
to be a Kaleido Star.
The show is starting soon,
would you like
to come and see it?
Huh? Is that okay?
Well, it's the least
I could do for you,
since you came all this way.
Wow, thank you.
Oh, by the way, I'm Ken.
So Ken took Sora
backstage to watch the show.
And that's when...
Hey look out!
She ended up injuring
one of the cast members.
By accident of course.
Then someone
unexpected showed up.
The boss.
The boss?
You will fill the role.
I-I...
She was actually going
to appear on stage.
But when the show started,
she didn't know whether
to be elated or terrified.
Lookout!
Oh, Sora.
No! I can't do it!
I can't perform!
I'm gonna fail.
Huh?
That's right.
I can't say that I can't do it.
I can do it.
Miss Rabbit!
I can't see below.
Sora!
Move it!
Yuri?
Just keep smiling
until the end.
Okay.
And so the show ended.
Sora had her chance to appear
on stage after all, but...
You're a naive little girl.
Don't you understand
that by now?
Yeah.
There's no place for you here.
Sora knew she
hadn't performed well.
And now it looked like her first
performance at Kaleido Stage
was destined to be her last.
Sora!
Huh?
Boss said that you passed!
You're passing
an unknown amateur
who didn't even audition?
Some day, the audience
will come here just to see
this little girl perform.
Now that the owner of Kaleido
Stage recognized her talent,
she was allowed
into the company.
Still, many more excruciating
ordeals were in store for her.
Hmm.
The Golden Phoenix.
Uh, good morning.
Yeah, if you like cleaning
that much, you can go ahead
and do all of ours
while you're at it.
Huh?
The company didn't like
that she'd been admitted
under special circumstances.
And on top of that,
Layla Hamilton made
a demand of her own.
Well, I didn't- I didn't mean...
Go ahead then... Why don't
show us your Golden Phoenix?
The Golden Phoenix-
an extremely difficult
maneuver only Layla could do.
...I won't acknowledge
your presence here.
You don't belong on the stage.
All right then. I'll do it!
I'll show you that I can
do the Golden Phoenix!
Really? I will
look forward to it.
Show me in a week,
but if you can't do it
after claiming so
boldly that you could,
you will leave here immediately.
Fine.
And so Sora's fight to gain
the company's acceptance
at Kaleido Stage began.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
If you fall, make sure you
land on your back. All right?
You don't have enough
momentum! Just let go!
Whew.
During the day she studied,
and at night she trained.
With this rigorous schedule,
she soon found it impossible
to hide her fatigue
from those around her.
Check her out.
She really must
be working hard.
Sora!
We brought you something!
We know you haven't
eaten anything.
And so, Sora's hard work
even won her the friendship
of some of her colleagues.
I can't believe
she's really doing it.
If only she could
grab that bar!
No, not yet.
She still can't keep a
beautiful pose in the air.
Even before she catches the bar,
what she is doing can't be
called a Golden Phoenix.
Go, Sora!
By tomorrow... It has to
be perfect it by tomorrow.
The day of Sora's test
had finally arrived.
I cannot wait to see
what kind of Golden Phoenix
she's going to show us.
I know.
I've gotta do it.
I must believe!
It was foolhardy for her
even to attempt it.
But would Sora be able to
complete the Golden Phoenix
and stay at
Kaleido Stage after all?
Her audience waited in
breathless anticipation.
Sora's entire future
depended on this moment.
This was a once
in a lifetime gamble.
The one I need to aim
for is not the bar.
My aim is my love.
My aim is Romeo.
And then...
Then I'll be Juliet!
The Golden Phoenix!
She did it!
Oh my G-
Sora, are you all right?
Yes, thank you.
You're really something.
Oh, Layla.
You didn't get
the last part right,
but it was definitely
the Golden Phoenix.
You deserve credit
for pulling it off.
Yuri, let's go.
Sora, you can stay
at Kaleido Stage!
And that is how Sora became
a member of Kaleido Stage.
Later, with her new
friends Anna and Mia,
she would learn how
to be a real company member.
And perhaps more importantly,
Sora would pass on her
newfound knowledge to others,
giving them a greater
love of the stage.
As with the lonely
little girl, Rosetta.
Who is she?
Don't you know?
She's that diabolo
prodigy from France.
She's great, a total genius!
Well, I'll see you later then.
I look forward to it.
Rosetta was extremely arrogant.
On stage, she gave the kind of
performance one would expect
from a world diabolo champion.
But it still left
something to be desired.
She is amazing.
But why isn't she
more fun to watch?
Watching her is like
watching a diabolo machine.
Mama, I'm bored!
I was going to
terminate your contract.
Oh.
I'm going to pay you
for the rest of this week,
but I don't want to
see you on stage again.
Those words hurt
Rosetta's pride.
Sora saw this and wanted
to do something for her.
She can do better if
you just let her try!
I'll give Rosetta another
shot on one condition.
Yes, what is it?
You do the show with her.
What's that?
Six days.
But Boss, wait!
I've never done
diabolo in my life.
But there was an
even bigger concern.
Would Rosetta even agree
to share the stage with Sora?
What was Kalos thinking,
pairing me with you?
I don't go on stage
to make mistakes.
What's the point of doing it
if you can't do it flawlessly?
Rosetta's words were harsh, but
they couldn't discourage Sora.
Ken, I think I've got an idea!
She performed on
the outdoor stage.
Catch!
Whoa, what's going on here?
Just jump in!
Caught it!
Haha she's so bad!
You're incredible, Sora!
Weird, isn't it?
What is?
When I watch her perform,
I get really nervous
she'll make a mistake.
I'm always on
the edge of my seat.
It's always so
exciting to watch her,
because she does
make a lot of mistakes.
But every once in a while,
she pulls off a trick,
and it's unbelievable.
Like magic!
You should go watch her tonight.
See what you think.
Watch Sora perform?
So Rosetta stayed to
see Sora's show that night.
Afterward, she was struck by the
audience's thunderous applause.
It's amazing.
Nothing like the
performances I give.
Sora!
Rosetta, you came
to see the show!
I want to perform diabolo with
you if you're still interested.
I'd like that!
And now, it's time for
Kaleido Stage's first
ever diabolo battle!
In this corner, we have the
world champion, Rosetta!
And in this corner,
with only five days diabolo
experience, is Sora.
Ready? Battle!
Lookin' good! Let's go, Sora!
You can do it, Rosetta!
Here!
And Rosetta wins it!
They sounded like
they'd never stop cheering.
At that moment,
Rosetta realized what
she should have known before:
that to please an audience is
the reason one should perform
in the first place.
Thanks for everything, Sora.
And then Sora moved
one step closer to
her goal of being a star.
An opportunity arose for her to
perform in the Little Mermaid.
Sora's talent and determination
caught the eye of an investor,
who insisted that she
be given a shot at the lead.
Amazing!
Her audition
went extremely well.
You're our new Kaleido Star.
Even Layla, who had been so
quick to dismiss Sora before,
had to acknowledge her talent.
I'm looking forward to it, too.
And so, Sora finally got
the chance to perform
with her idol, Layla.
However, the difference in
their skill level was obvious.
One, two, three...
They couldn't seem to
get their timing right.
Sorry!
So Layla took unexpected action.
Yes?
But Layla, what are you-?
I leave you kids to it.
Thank you.
Yeah, okay.
So, what's up?
I'm going to be staying
with you, if you don't mind.
Wha-?
Oh, that's just-
That's exactly why I came here.
I need to observe the way
you move in day-to-day life.
By living in close quarters,
I hope we can understand
each other's movements better.
So we understand each
other's movements better.
Right.
Sora! Wanna get some food?
And thus was the start
of their new partnership.
Sora tried hard to adjust
herself to Layla's pace,
even though she was
unsure of herself.
However,
there weren't many
days left until
the opening of the show.
Their performance was
far from being perfect.
And around that time...
Jump!
That was too close!
I think we should
tone down the climax,
or else the show's
gonna blow up in our faces.
So you're saying you wanna
make the fight scene easy?
Yes.
Unacceptable.
But Layla, I'm-
We can't hold
back on the climax.
The show'll fall apart.
All we need is one more day.
They only had one day left.
They had to make
a drastic move.
Excuse me, but-
We're going to
practice out here.
What?
Having the fight
be perfect isn't enough.
It's the same kind of choice
I've been making
on stage for years.
What are you saying?
This has to be a real fight,
between the two of us.
A real fight?
Between me and Layla?
So what?
Will you do it or not?
Right.
Then, their real life fight
without a lifeline began.
She's really
serious about this!
If I drop my guard
for one second,
she's gonna toss
me into the ocean!
Make that mistake again,
and you're gonna be shark bait.
But what fate had in store,
neither could possibly foresee.
One more day until
the opening of their show.
Sora and Layla's intense
training continued even during
a violent storm.
They're like... machines.
Are you ready to give up yet?
No way!
Oh, really?
No, Miss Hamilton!
You still in one piece?
Yeah!
Then the day of
their opening arrived.
Would their first performance
together be a success?
Sora!
Thank you, Layla.
It's been a really long time
since I've heard the
audience applaud like this.
I'm so happy!
I don't know what to say.
I don't want this
moment to ever end!
Through her performance with
Layla, Sora had grown up a lot.
But she had just started down
the path to becoming a star.
She still knew very little
about the kind of
ordeals that lay ahead.
Kaleido Stage is going
to be taken over by Yuri.
Suddenly, Layla and Sora's
partnership is jeopardized.
What will happen
to Sora's dream now?
Then, Sora flies to the
Grand Canyon and embarks on
a rigorous training
regimen with Layla
in order to attempt the
Legendary Great Maneuver,
a move which has cost
many performers their lives.
What will happen?
Next time on Kaleido Star:
'Amazing Prologue to Stardom.'