Hey everyone,
Kaleido Star's about to start,
so make sure that
your room is brightly lit,
and that you're not
sitting too close to the TV.
I know it's a little late, but
happy New Year everybody!
Well, well, well.
How did you spend
your New Year's Day?
Shrine visits?
A New Year's meal?
Did you get New Year's gifts?
As for me, well I'm
not feeling too festive.
My little sister
was born last year,
and this will be our
first New Year's together.
I should be happy,
but I'm still so upset.
There's nothing
I can do about it now.
Things can't stay like this
forever, but, but, but...
You two did a
great job out there.
Followed by Layla
and Yuri's success,
we were able to secure
two consecutive wins.
Good work.
I want you to
start rehearsing for
the New Year's show immediately.
In fact, let's start tomorrow.
This show will be your
triumphal performance.
Needless to say, I want to see
the Demon Spiral as a climax.
You got that, Mia?
Yes sir.
Excuse me...but about Sora?
Sora!
Is Sora going to be onstage?
The festival
contest isn't over yet.
I can't believe you withdrew.
You're the worst.
You disgraced the festival.
You ran away from the stage.
A serious match
was taking place.
It's a place where you
destroy the dreams of others.
I told myself I would
fight to the finish.
I'm so ashamed.
But in the end, I just...
I'm disappointed in you Sora.
I'm sorry for the trouble
that I caused you.
Amazing and Sad Homecoming.
Hey boss, Sora's gone!
Yes, I know.
What?!
Let Mia know.
We'll have to recast Sora's role
in the New Year's show.
And here I am back home.
'Kay.
Sora?
But Sora?
I...I um, I'm home.
Well welcome home Sora.
Please don't shock
me like that again.
You could at least call to let
me know you're coming home.
Sorry.
It's just so unexpected.
Um well...I thought...since it's
New Year's and everything...
But Sora, don't your rehearsals
start right after the New Year?
Yeah...well...I decided
to skip it this time.
Skip rehearsal?
Did something happen?
Uh uh, nothing.
I can't believe
Yume's gotten so big.
I came home Yume.
I'm your big sister.
I just thought that once she
has the baby... once she has a
baby of her own she
won't need me anymore.
Sora.
Your mother and the baby
are working hard in there.
Let's cheer them on.
And Sora.
Yes?
I'd like for you
to name your sister.
Are you sure you want me to?
I've always wanted
you to name my baby.
Oh.
Thank you Yume.
Because of you
I finally feel like
I've become a
part of the family.
My mom and dad would
love for me to stay at home.
I think I'll just
stay here forever.
I won't go back
to the stage anymore.
Hello, Naegino residence?
I...don't understand.
One moment please.
Sora?
Someone named
Mia's on the phone.
She's one of your
friends I met, right?
Hello?
Mia?
Sora!
Hey everyone, I found her!
Really?
Thank goodness!
Sorry, you're worried about me?
Of course, you left
without telling us!
Um...well there's a lot of stuff
I wanna think over. And...
Hey Sora, you're
coming back aren't ya?
Yeah, when are you coming back?
We're all waiting for you!
Well I...I'm doing just fine,
so don't worry about me.
Thanks for checking
in with me though.
Bye.
Sora!
Well well.
I never thought I'd come
home to see you here.
For a moment I
thought I was dreaming.
You're exaggerating.
So, are you gonna be
staying for a while?
I've worked hard, and I deserve
some time off, you know?
I think you're right.
Midori, would you mind getting
me another beer please?
My my, two in one night?
It's been a while since
the whole family's
been together, that's
reason to celebrate, right?
Yes, it is.
Back in my own room.
Which five year old girl
does this room belong to?
Fool!
You were hiding in my
luggage weren't you?
I always meant to come
to Japan at least once.
If only to check
out the geisha's
and the pretty young girls.
You shouldn't bother with me.
You're wasting your time.
Hmm?
The stage...I'm not...
So you've decided that
you're not going back?
That's right.
I see.
Well...we'll just see
how things play out.
If you have given
up the stage,
then soon you will lose
the ability to see me.
Demon...Spiral!
Don't look so down Mia.
I'm sure that Sora
will be back soon.
Excuse me?
Don't just stand there!
If you don't start
giving me some direction,
I won't know what's going on.
Oh...um...I'm sorry.
Are you trying to make
Leon and I look bad?
If you don't wanna
work, then quit.
What's up with her?
She thinks she's so special.
There's nothing we can do.
I mean she's number
one in the world, right?
Yeah but she's too confident.
Maybe it's all an act.
Well...it's nice not
to have that girl around.
Happy New Year everyone!
This is the most lavish
New Year's meal we've ever had!
Mom your ozouni
soup, it's to die for!
Well have as much as you'd like.
Looks like we've made
it to Sora's home town.
You know it's
not that bad a place.
I was really hoping
to come here alone.
There's no time
to space out Ken.
You came to see Sora, right?
But all I know is
her street address.
I don't know...
how to find her house.
Kid I'm a police officer.
Just let me handle it.
Happy New Year.
Sora why don't you take a bath.
I think you should
begin the New Year
by cleansing your body,
and maybe even...
Fool, how long are
you gonna stick around?
I already told you I'm not going
back to the Kaleido Stage.
Why don't you go and
find someone else?
If that's true, then why
are you still training?
I'm just stretching to
work off that meal!
I see.
Then you should take a shower
since you've gotten all
sweaty exercising.
Sora!
The phone's for you!
Coming!
That certainly didn't work
the way I'd planned it.
Who is it?
It's Miss Kurata.
It's Manami?
Manami!
Hey, how are you?
I can't believe you Sora.
You could have at
least called to let me
know that you're in town.
Yeah, sorry.
I'm coming over
with Sayaka and Miki.
So how about a New Year's
party at your place?
Uh yeah, sure.
Hey!
Could you please
tell me where...
Not again.
I tell you, these Japanese
are a bunch of weirdos.
Well um...maybe it's just your
approach that isn't working.
Why don't you
let me give it a try.
Excuse me ladies?
Check him out!
Who is he?
He looks super cool!
Wow, maybe he's some
super famous soccer
player or something!
No way, he's an
American movie star!
Yeah, he's cute,
let's take pictures!
Uhh excuse me?
I've got a question!
Do any of you know Sora!
Sora!
Happy New Year Sora,
from all of us!
Oh it's been so long you guys!
Please make yourselves at home.
Thank you Mrs. Naegino.
I have to tell you Sora,
I never thought that
you'd actually go to America.
Oh, really?
It's just so hard to believe.
I was surprised too.
I knew that being a
Kaleido star was your dream,
but you really did it!
Manami, you got to see
Sora's show, didn't you?
Yeah.
I saw the legendary
great maneuver.
So tell us, what was it like?
Umm, well, how do I begin?
I felt like I was flying
in the sky with them.
It's strange, but I felt
like I was getting this
surge of positive energy
just from watching them.
It was...amazing.
Wow.
I wish I could see it.
You're getting to perform
and play leading roles,
I'm so jealous!
What?
Oh yeah, Sayaka's an
up and coming voice actor.
What?
That's so cool!
You're voicing anime?
Well I'm trying.
In fact, in the last round of
auditions I even made it to
the final callbacks
for the leading role...
but I didn't get the part.
Don't give up!
There will be other
shows to audition for.
Yeah.
Well, I guess I just have
to work on my skills, huh?
Hey Miki, whatever
happened to your dreams
of being a manga artist?
I've decided to
go to junior college
and get a real job
like everyone else.
I still draw all the time,
but it's just a hobby now.
But Miki,
you're such a good artist!
That's such a waste.
When something you
love becomes your job
it gets kinda tough you know?
I just love manga so much that
I don't ever wanna
grow to hate it.
It's the one thing
I've always enjoyed,
and I don't wanna lose it.
Miki, you're such a realist!
I guess.
So what about you Sora,
your dreams have all come true.
Yeah, but why do
you look so down?
Well...I don't...I just don't
know how to explain.
Hey, why don't you
show us a few tricks.
Will you please?
It is New Year's after all.
Please Sora?
Okay.
That's so cool!
How are you able
to do that Sora?
Wow!
You're so awesome!
This applause...
it's different from the
applause at the festival.
But what makes it so different?
That's so cool!
The audience is applauding
for the same reason.
So, have I changed?
I'm having fun.
I enjoy performing for
Manami and my friends.
That's it!
A show that everyone enjoys!
That's the Kaleido
Stage that I love.
That's the kind of
show I want to be in.
Tadaa!
Bravo!
I can tell you're a real pro!
Well we have to go
this way to get home.
Okay.
I promise to come
see your show one day.
Me too, me too!
See ya Sora!
Bye!
I've decided to go to college.
Don't get me wrong, I'm not
giving up my dream of
becoming a hair stylist;
I've just decided to take
some time to talk it
over with my parents.
Thanks to you
I've started thinking
a lot about my future,
and about chasing my dreams.
Because of me?
That's right.
I watched you work so hard
trying to achieve your dream,
and that inspired me
to follow my dreams too.
Sora, you helped me.
You gave me a dream.
Gave you a dream?
Why did you come home?
Does it have anything
to do with you quitting
in the middle of a circus
festival performance?
How do you know about that?
I read about it on the internet.
Yeah.
But that's not the only reason.
Your mom was
worried sick about you.
What?!
She called me and asked me to
spend some time with you
to get your mind off...
whatever was bothering you.
What are you so upset about?
Well I...Manami I walked
out of the Kaleido Stage.
I think that's fine.
I mean, as long as you
don't have any regrets.
Back in school you always
said that you liked to go out
and do things rather
than thinking about them.
You told me that thinking about
stuff might make you hesitant.
And then you wouldn't
do it, and you'd regret it.
So if you've made your
decision and have no regrets,
then I have no problem with it.
But if you have even a bit
of regret in your heart...
then you should go
back to Kaleido Stage
and give it another shot.
Just walk up to them and say
"I've changed my mind and
I wanna come back".
You're the only person
I know that can do that Sora.
And I think that's cool.
Manami...
Remember when I
came to visit in America,
and I told you that I came to
see your regretful face?
Yeah?
This may sound selfish,
but I don't wanna see your
regretful face right now.
Ahhhhh!
What were you thinking,
swallowing that man whole?
I guess I'm gonna have to
leave without even seeing her.
You'd better watch out lion,
or I'm gonna tear you to pieces.
Mr Policeman?!
Oh, Sora!
I've been looking for you!
I even brought
Ken as a tagalong.
Oh you did!
I'm...a tagalong...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make
everyone worry so much.
We've wrapped rehearsals
on the New Year's shows,
so I came out here to find you.
The New Year's show?
May and Leon's
triumphal performance.
Since tomorrow's opening day,
I'm afraid I have to leave now.
What!
But Ken, you just got here!
Unfortunately, we
already purchased our
plane tickets for the trip home!
I see.
You're coming back, aren't you?
Sora...I hope you didn't...
If I go back to Kaleido
Stage feeling like this,
I'm afraid I'll just get
in everyone's way.
Well when you
dropped out of the festival,
I was actually
a little relieved.
I was relieved that you
chose to drop out rather
than continue with
something you felt wasn't right.
You did the right thing.
If you don't like
to compete,
create a show
without competition.
Create a show?
Myself?
I wanna see more
of your fun show, Sora.
When I watch you fly by with a
smile it makes me feel happy,
and I just want...
to tell you... that I...
I like you, Sora.
Ken...
And I like you lots too.
I like seeing you smile
as you fly through the air.
As your first fan,
I'd be thrilled to see
an exciting new show
starring Sora.
Right Mr. Second Fan?
Second fan?!
Just remember that all of your
fans are behind you 100%.
But...what I meant was...
We love you Sora!
I'm going to create
a fun Kaleido Stage
show with no more competition.
I want you to be my dream.
You have what it takes
to be a true Kaleido Star.
The answer to all of these are
to be found inside of you.
Go after your dream,
and don't let yourself get lost.
If you do that,
the road to becoming a
Kaleido Star will
appear for you.
That's it!
I'm going to create a
Kaleido Stage show
with no competition
that's fun for everyone.
That's my real dream.
If I can do that,
then it won't be long 'til I
finally become a Kaleido Star!
Is something wrong?
Thank you Ken!
I've decided that I'm gonna
go back to the Kaleido Stage.
I promise you.
We'll be waiting.
And when you make
it back to the states
I'll pick you up at the airport.
Thanks you guys!
I see.
Yeah, I think that's great.
Thank you, Manami.
You did the same for me.
Let's do our best.
So that's the real
reason I came home.
I'm sorry.
I hope you're not mad.
I know it's a pathetic
story but after a lot of
thinking I've decided
to go back...and well...
Midori?
This is for you Sora.
What is it?
Since you didn't get to visit
the shrine this New Year's...
A good luck charm.
Please take
good care of yourself.
Oh thank you.
Don't ever stop trying
'til you're satisfied.
Yume, I'm gonna do my best,
and be a good example...
Oh Yume, you're silly!
One more time,
I'm gonna try one more time.
And this time I won't
lose sight of my dream.
Never.
Seems like the fog
of confusion has cleared.
Thanks for waiting everyone!
My name is
Sora Naegino, and I'm back!
I really appreciate
everyone waiting for me.
This time I've got the
confidence and the
determination to make
my dreams come true.
And no one's gonna stop me.
No one, no one!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"My Amazing Fresh Start"!
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky.