Performers will be drawn here
by their admiration of you.
When that happens,
you must always meet
your challengers head on.
And when your time is up,
you must fight with all your
strength to accept defeat.
Competing with your
challengers will be
an important duty of yours.
Don't forget that.
Okay.
Layla's right.
I can't even imagine
a world without competition.
There's always gonna
be some kind of problem
going on in the world.
But I still think it'd be nice
if there wasn't any competition
on the stage at least.
Challengers.
Adventurers.
Pioneers.
All who are called
by such names are fools.
What awaits the fool who pursues
the dream that no-one dares
to dream is either
applause or scorn.
Please be my dream.
Sora?
To The Amazing Promised Place.
Bye mom and dad!
I'll see you tomorrow!
You bet!
I can't wait to see the show!
Ken, are you sure
your parents don't mind?
I mean they're taking
in my whole family.
Well my mom's the one that
offered, so it must be okay.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Tomorrow's opening day, finally.
You know they still haven't
finished construction.
Yeah.
But it's a big
construction project.
Don't worry about it Mia.
We're almost finished.
Thanks.
I'm so sorry.
You know, you should really stop
apologizing for everything.
You gave us a job
to be excited about.
I'm actually kinda grateful.
This is gonna be
our best set ever.
I'm counting on you Jean!
Do you know if May and Rosetta's
maneuver was accepted?
The directorial team
was supposed to decide
at yesterday's rehearsal.
But Cathy decided
to test them again today.
I guess it'll be okay.
But Rosetta I'd like to see
a more commanding presence
from you tomorrow.
Can you pull it off?
Of course I can.
That's great!
Did Anna's clown team
make it in too?
Yeah.
You... you mean...
We get to... perform?
I'm so happy!
That special training
really paid off!
I can't breathe.
I'm serious guys!
So that means
everyone got their dream.
But... why aren't you
performing anymore?
Me?
Why do you ask?
Well, I thought you really
wanted to be a performer.
I mean, it seemed like you
were having so much fun
as a clown on Anna's team.
I thought "Hooray,
congratulations!"
But now...
That was a dream
from a long time ago.
It's not my dream now.
Oh, it isn't?
Oh I forgot to tell you.
I heard that our opening day
show is sold out.
Really!
Yeah.
I was kinda worried
because curtain is at
such an unusual time.
But that didn't seem to matter.
You know, Yuri's the one
who worked out our tie-in
with the tour groups.
Well well.
So he has his father's
sound business sense?
I think he'll make a good
partner for you, Kalos.
I need to confess
something to you.
Confess what?!
You see Ken...
Yeah?
I'm kinda full of myself.
What are you talking about?!
Could you explain please?
Well, I thought that the reason
you were always helping me
was because you thought I could
help you achieve your dream.
Don't get me wrong, I know
the reason you help me so much
is cuz I'm always
desperately in need of help.
I understand that, really.
But when I think
about helping you,
it motivates me and
gives me strength.
So I've been letting
myself believe that.
Ken, it's thanks to you
that I've been able
to make it this far.
Thank you so much.
You're not full
of yourself, Sora.
From now on
you'll be responsible
for all kinds of dreams.
Not just mine or your
friends, but lots of peoples.
We should probably get going.
We've got to get plenty
of rest for tomorrow.
Yeah, let's go.
A stage with no competition.
Well it's definitely
a long shot.
But as I get older
I really wanna believe
in those impossible dreams.
I've been told the only people
who can become true stars
are the ones who pursue
their dreams, even though
they know they're foolish.
It's got to be difficult
to know your dream is foolish.
The day of the audition,
everyone began reliving
their memories.
It was as if Sora's
performance brought them on.
They were memories of
when we wanted to smile.
And make others smile with us.
Her talent... it's the talent
of a true Kaleido Star.
A talent she
discovered on her own.
I'm sure the audience's
hearts will become one.
Don't you think so?
Do you really wanna
know what I think?
I think it's wrong
that you were practicing
the "Angel's Maneuver"
without even telling me.
Oh, I'm sorry Cathy.
Wow, that threw me off.
I don't think I've
ever heard you apologize.
So you wanna
take my car tomorrow?
I'm not going to
the show tomorrow.
What?
But why not?
I already know Sora's going
to become a true Kaleido Star.
I don't have to see it.
Besides, I really don't want
to look like a sore loser
that's posing as her guardian.
Okay...
So you lost the competition.
Big deal!
I mean you're still
the same Layla Hamilton
she's always admired, right?
I think you should go
and support her.
Okay, I'll go.
That was fast!
What's with you today,
you're freaking me out!
There's nothing with me,
you just give good advice.
Really?
I didn't know you
appreciated my advice.
But I'll give it to you anyway.
Do me a favor,
can you stay like this after
we get back to Broadway?
Sorry, I can't promise anything.
I figured as much.
Listen I really think you should
come see the show tomorrow.
I have a weird feeling
that something special
is gonna happen.
Something special?
Yeah, I have a feeling.
And now the "Angel's Maneuver"!
Jump!
Hey, it's Sora!
Welcome back Sora!
I'm home again!
Did you miss me
while I was gone?
Sure did!
It's really boring around here
cuz everyone's at
practice right now.
They're at practice?
Then I should go too!
Sora?
Yeah, what is it?
You need to get some rest.
Well, yeah, but I...
Everyone watched you struggle to
perfect the "Angel's Maneuver",
so they're doing their
best to catch up with you.
You deserve to have a night off.
Don't worry, they're
working really hard!
You're right.
Sora!
I've made a decision.
I'm going to audition
for the Kaleido Stage
and become a performer like you.
Really!
Jonathan says he'll try too,
he's got nothing to lose.
That's great!
What?!
You understand him?!
Do your best tomorrow Sora!
--Umm goodnight!
--See ya later!
Well, I'm gonna get going too.
Sure.
Thanks a lot Ken!
A stage without
competition, huh?
I had heard that you like
to inspect the trapeze
the night before a show.
I guess it's true.
What do you want Yuri?
I thought we could talk.
We're two people who
couldn't become demons.
So you are right.
I'm not capable
of becoming a demon.
Did you come here just
to say "I told you so"?
You know on a basic level,
the "Angel's Maneuver"
can be performed alone.
You and I are just
there... for support.
For support?
Layla and Sora are strong.
They can do anything
they put their mind to.
But sometimes,
even the strongest woman
needs someone to lean on.
Our job is to support
them during those times.
That's our role, Leon.
So then, we are the angels?
I guess you're right.
Maybe that's why we
couldn't become demons.
Manami, Sayaka, and Miki
are all gonna be there.
That's great.
Do you think Yume's old enough
to understand the show?
I take it you can't sleep.
Uh huh.
But I'll try to sleep since
I've got to be ready
to give it my all tomorrow.
Well then, goodnight.
Goodnight.
The "Angel's Maneuver"?
Wow.
I've heard that it's sometimes
called the "Fool's Maneuver".
Well, according to the program
the story's about Odette
and her battle for
the prince's love.
So basically it's
about a girl having
a tough time
dating a popular guy.
Odette is convinced that
everyone has an angel heart,
deep inside,
even the evil Odile.
That sounds like Sora.
Are you excited Yume?
She's in a good mood.
We could have waited for
the afternoon showing Tim.
I'm fine!
I need glasses.
When's the show gonna start?
It's like, a full house,
even though it's so early.
They say there's
some special reason for
these early morning
performances.
I really wanted to see
your Odette, Miss Layla.
I'm happy to say that I'll never
stand on that stage again.
Did you invite anyone
to the show, Leon?
I sent Alan passes
and plane tickets,
but he probably sold
them to buy alcohol.
He wouldn't do that...
I don't think.
I'm sure your old partners
will be in the audience
to get their smiles back.
I bet they'll be glad to see
that you're doing so well.
Do you really believe in a stage
without any competition?
I've decided to believe in it.
You can't perform the
"Legendary Great Maneuver"
unless you believe
it in your heart.
And the "Angel's Maneuver"
is the same way.
By the way,
I owe you an apology.
Yeah... huh?
Apology for what?
When I said Layla was
a lukewarm performer,
you told me to
apologize, didn't you?
Oh yeah.
I thought she retired after
performing the "legendary
Great Maneuver" with you so that
she could leave on a high note.
So she would be the closest
to a true Kaleido Star.
But she mastered
the "Angel's Maneuver"
by herself and came back.
And, she was prepared to lose.
For your sake.
She did it for me?
If you hadn't competed
against Layla that day,
you wouldn't be as secure and
confident as you are right now.
Yeah, you're right.
Okay everyone, it's time
to raise the curtain.
Let's make this the greatest
show they've ever seen!
And now it's Scene 5.
This is where Odette
meets the prince.
The prince falls in love.
Wow, Leon's really into it!
Of course he is,
the material is great!
Scene 11.
The Ball.
Here comes Anna's clown team.
Oh wow!
Anna looks amazing!
It's time for her
special training to
finally be put to the test.
Don't go!
They're laughing!
It looks like she's
being pulled by a string,
but there's nothing there.
How funny!
Come back!
They think I'm funny!
Mom?
Dad?
I finally did it.
Congratulations, Anna.
The next scene is Demon Lake.
The prince has his
heart stolen by Odile!
Odile has a demon heart.
She's mysterious and bold.
And more dynamic than Odette!
She's so pretty!
We love you big sister!
Okay, set change
to the dark forest.
Odile leads the prince
into the dark forest
and they become trapped there.
Meanwhile, Odette notices
the conflict in Odile's heart.
Then a fairy leads Odile
back from her path of despair.
I'm counting on you, Rosetta.
I'm gonna give them the
greatest show they've ever seen.
Okay, it's time for
"Eternal Illusion".
"Eternal... Illusion"!
Pretty good, kid.
Thank you, May.
And now it's time.
Scene 32.
The angel's flight.
We have to believe
in Sora's angel.
Three minutes and counting.
Okay, start opening the gate.
This is the part where
Sora becomes an angel.
Go forth, ye fool.
Continue to believe
that what awaits you
in the end is applause.
How beautiful.
That's our Sora?
She did it!
Now, lower the angel trapeze.
I'll show my angel
heart to everyone.
I hope that everyone
who came here today...
I hope that their angel
hearts will become one.
It's funny.
I always thought of a
performance as an ordeal.
I would try to get through it
as quickly as possible.
But when I'm performing
on stage with Sora...
I treasure my time
on stage with her.
She makes every moment
of her performance seem
irreplaceably precious.
I wish that you would enjoy
your time on stage, Leon.
If I become a true star,
I'm sure it'll change you too.
You know, no moment on stage
is ever the same twice.
There's no time
like the present.
So I chose to live in the
present and enjoy every moment.
That way,
I'll never have regrets.
Sophie.
I finally understand what
you were trying to say.
Suddenly... I wanna
go back on stage.
I wanna perform with Sora.
Yeah, me too.
All of a sudden... I feel weird.
Yeah, me too,
I can't stand still.
Sora!
May!
Rosetta!
It can't be.
Mute!
I wanna perform
with a true star.
Then come on.
Let's go!
You wanna go too Jonathan?
But... I didn't think
this was possible.
It's amazing.
Even the most
competitive performers.
They're all on stage
performing together as one.
You should go.
Yeah!
This is the stage
Sora dreamed of.
Here, in this moment.
A stage with no
competition exists.
Sora.
I'm glad I was here
to witness your miracle.
My role is over now, isn't it?
It's Layla!
You've shown me
the impossible, Sora.
Your dream has come true.
You're a true Kaleido Star.
Sora!
You're the best!
Bravo!
I knew you could do it, Sora!
So the dream has
become a reality.
I'm a little sad it's over.
But it's not over yet, Yuri.
This is the start
of a new dream.
Well, I should be going.
Okay.
Um, Layla?
Do you think it's
alright if... if I continue
to think of myself
as your dream?
No Sora.
I'm afraid you cannot
be my dream anymore.
Live your own dream.
You've become my pride and joy.
Thank you Layla.
I will.
Miss Layla?
I turned in my resignation as a
Hamilton family maid yesterday.
I've decided I'm going to
chase my dream of performing
on Broadway.
I hope you'll allow me
to accompany you.
That's fine.
Let's get going.
Yes ma'am!
It... must be my imagination...
And so the dream is
passed on to the next fool.
The dream of becoming
a true Kaleido Star.
I heard the shows sold out
for the next two months.
Isn't that awesome?
That makes me so happy!
I wonder if I can
be in the show too!
Is something wrong, Rosetta?
It's nothing...
If you don't wanna yell "Eternal
Illusion", just tell her.
What are you yammering about?
Calm down!
My wings are my dream,
and on toward the sky!