Okay everyone, Kaleido
Star's about to begin.
Make sure your room
is brightly lit while
you're watching Kaleido Star,
and please sit as far away
from the TV as you can.
Well well well, you've all
given someone a present, right?
You know how you wonder
if they'll like it?
You put all your feelings
into picking a gift out
for that special someone.
My gift to people
is performing on stage.
I hope everyone that sees
a Kaleido Stage show
can walk away with a smile.
And I hope the other performers
who work with me feel like
they've been a part of
something great too.
That would be so awesome,
wouldn't it?
I am a Kaleido Star, I am, I am!
98...
Practicing during the day
isn't enough for you?
It's nowhere near enough.
The Amazing Injured Swan.
If you keep pushing yourself,
it's gonna continue to hurt.
I know.
You're forcing your body
to compensate for
the basics you lack.
That's why your feet
are in so much pain.
You know he's right, Sora.
Your center of
gravity is unstable,
so you're compensating
by overworking your toes.
These blood blisters are huge.
I'm afraid you're gonna have to
rest your feet for a few days.
I don't have time to rest...
Okay, fine.
Can I at least
protect the injured areas
so you don't put
too much weight on them?
That would be great, thank you.
We should probably start
working on your balance.
I'll put that on
your training schedule.
One, two, three.
Cathy?
I've got a quick
question for you.
What is it?
What scene will
Rosetta be performing in?
None of them.
She's not in the show?
It wasn't our choice.
There was originally a diabolo
scene written into the script,
but she said she wouldn't
have anything to do with it.
Mia wrote it specifically for
Rosetta, but since she doesn't
want to perform diabolo
we cut the scene.
It really wasn't
necessary anyway.
Does Sora know about this?
Yeah.
Stop everyone.
I'm sorry about this,
but I'm gonna have to rethink
this combination again.
Drop this for now, just switch
to individual practice please.
This is the third time.
Hey!
If you guys don't mind,
there's someone I want
to introduce you to.
My feet hurt, but I feel
like I'm getting somewhere.
All this practice is paying off.
I wanna keep practicing.
Sorry I'm late!
We'll resume your
training this afternoon.
Go.
You should rest until then.
Well, okay.
Welcome all you homely,
I mean, beautiful housewives.
Okay ladies,
save those vacant looks for
your old tired husbands.
When you're with me,
I wanna see your wild side.
Cuz I know that's
not gonna happen!
You'd think there'd be
some kind of training gear
that could help Sora
with her problems.
This chap's brutal.
But he's got this strange
charm and rugged good looks.
I just can't seem
to make myself hate him.
Clean finish leaves any
surface squeaky clean.
From your kids doodles to the
little secret you've been
hiding from your husband.
It all wipes away.
Come on.
Can't you help me
out a little bit?
Why are you boring us with
this garbage, Junk Baron?
This stuff's not garbage,
it's treasure!
Hey, that's Anna's dad!
What?!
But Anna doesn't
look anything like him!
Our next treasure
helps firm flabby flesh.
Try a pair of
these crazy shoes on.
Don't lose your balance!
That's it!
Hey Jack!
Sorry I'm late.
Hey Anna.
It's the real Jack Baron!
I'm glad.
It sounds like work
is going well.
Yeah.
In fact, I just met with the
producers at the comedy channel.
They want me to do
a half hour program.
Oh wow, cool!
So you're pretty
busy right now, huh?
But you know I've
always got time for you.
I can't refuse
a request from my savior.
I could get hit by lightning.
She's your savior?
Anna is my own little angel.
Okay, I'm ready.
So is the lesson, like,
finally gonna start?
It sure took them long enough.
Maybe that's because
they're close to perfecting
the "Angel's Maneuver".
This is the final
stage of training for
the "Angel's Maneuver".
Already?!
I knew it!
What is the matter?
Let's get started.
Right.
I'm gonna change the way I
channel my strength every time.
You're going to have to sense
that and adjust for it.
Okay.
We should report to Miss Layla.
Let's go.
Like, we're outta here.
Can we do it again please?
Rosetta?
Yeah, what?
Tell me; is it true that
you're not going to be
performing in Swan Lake?
That's true.
This is an important show
for Sora and I didn't
want to get in the way.
The diabolo scene
was unnecessary.
Hmm.
How mature of you.
But if you don't wanna perform,
why are you peeking in
on everyone's rehearsal?
That's none of your
business, is it May?
If you wanna perform,
why don't you just tell them?
I can't.
I've already made my decision.
Amazing.
The "Angel's Maneuver" is
really starting to take shape.
But, Sora's balance seems
to be getting worse and worse.
It's possible for an ugly guy
to play a handsome man.
I'll tell you what,
makeup can do wonders.
But when you look as good as
me there's nothing you can do!
You can push
anything over the top,
and all of a sudden...
it's funny.
Our set design is being
outdone by Sora's energy.
I mean right now it's
a nice little set up
that does what we
need... but that's it!
The only people who will accept
this kind of textbook
construction are the critics.
It has to be more.
Now hold that
pose and maintain it.
Okay.
That's enough.
The "Angel's Maneuver"
training is over.
Leon, what do you
mean it's over?!
The "Angel's Maneuver"
has been perfected.
I suggest you fine tune it,
and rest your body
until opening day.
Perfected?
You're just saying that!
I can keep going, Leon!
Please wait!
It's over already?
It can't be...
You're breaking off the
"Angel's Maneuver" training?
At the current level
she can maintain it for
at least five minutes.
And if she saves her strength,
I'm sure she can manage
the two daily shows.
It's enough.
Can you really call that
the "Angel's Maneuver"?
She lacks basic balance.
She's compensating by
forcibly holding the poses
with her leg strength.
So in that sense,
it's not the real thing.
But the audience won't know.
That doesn't satisfy me Leon.
If she overextends herself,
the show will fail miserably.
I've got it covered.
You just use this time
to work on publicity,
and then you can sit back
and rake in the profits.
Will you be able to make good
on that promise to your
little sister like that?
That is none of your business.
Sora!
What happened?
Where's Leon?
He said my special
training was over.
Oh I see.
But that can't be right.
He gave up on me.
I'm sure that's not true.
Let me take a look at your feet.
Sora!
What have you done!
Your balance kept getting worse,
so I knew something was up.
You've torn the
skin off your toes!
If you've come this far
and Leon's given you the okay,
isn't that enough?
No, it's not enough!
I won't give up!
I'll keep going!
There's no way I can wake up
everyone's angel heart
with a maneuver
that isn't perfected.
Her special training is over?
Yes ma'am.
That's definitely
what Mr. Leon said.
Then Sora...
She, like, totally
didn't accept that.
Really...
Miss Layla,
you're so beautiful!
According to their reports,
Leon has minimized
her balance training.
He spent that time
strengthening her legs instead.
It seems he's trying to
modify the "Angel's Maneuver"
into something Sora can do
at her current ability level.
But Sora would
never accept a fake.
She would never do
something half-heartedly
just to keep up appearances.
Well, if Leon can't
completely become a demon,
there's only one way left.
The angel herself will
have to become a demon.
Sora.
You're cutting the
"Angel's Maneuver"?!
You can't do that!
We'll have to rework
the entire stage!
But isn't Sora making progress?
We're making her get
treatment for her feet.
She's ripped the
skin off her toes.
There's no way she can
perform in that condition.
Kalos...
I can still go on.
I can still do it.
Are your feet
feeling any better?
This is ridiculous.
I'll be back.
Wait a minute Sora,
where are you going?
I'm going to ask Leon
to continue my training.
One last time.
Sora!
Oh my, you startled me!
Sarah!
I'm sorry.
I have a delivery!
A present from a sensitive man.
You got me a present, Ken?
It's no big deal,
I was just looking for a way
to help you out, that's all.
Woah!
I bought some too,
I couldn't resist!
I thought I'd recommend
them to Leon to help with
improving her balance.
They won't put too much of
a burden on her feet either.
I'm definitely going to ask Leon
to continue my special training.
So I'll recommend them too.
They're great!
My special training
isn't over yet!
What are you doing out here?
I thought I told you
to rest, Sora.
I have a request: I want you
to continue my training.
I'm begging you.
There's no need.
The "Angel's Maneuver"
has been perfected.
But I know that's not true!
Right now I'm doing all I can
just to fake the appearance
of the "Angel's Maneuver".
And it's nowhere near perfect!
I don't feel right about lying
to the audience like that.
If I say it's over,
then it's over.
If you won't help me, I'll
continue training by myself.
What?
I'm going to keep
training until I'm satisfied.
I swear that I'll perfect
the "Angel's Maneuver"
before opening day.
Then I'll finally
get you to acknowledge me.
Do what you want.
There's a limit to the
amount of pain a person
can put themselves through.
Now who's the fool?
Oh shut up.
It's obviously gonna take
some practice to get used to.
But if I can incorporate balance
training into my daily life,
then eventually I...
The fool aims for
heights, yet unseen.
First, we have to get you used
to the feel of the shoes.
Right!
Rosetta, can you get some water?
Sure!
Your balance has gotten
a lot better, huh?
Yeah, it has!
It seems that the special
training isn't over.
It's exactly like
Miss Layla predicted.
Head's up!
So how's it feel, Sora?
Awesome!
Since I've been wearing
these shoes I can tell that
I've been overworking my leg
muscles while I was training.
Okay, time to switch legs now.
This is how it should feel.
I just have to get here
without these shoes.
Here's another one!
Okay!
Don't let your pose slip.
Right!
Rosetta.
And if all goes well,
I'm gonna start doing balance
training again tomorrow.
You're fired up, huh?
Will you be able to do the
"Angel's Maneuver" by opening?
I should if I keep practicing.
I promise I'll do my best.
I really want Leon
to acknowledge me.
I know that you can do it, Sora!
I'll keep
practicing trapeze too.
Then, maybe someday, I'll get
to perform on stage with you.
I look forward to it.
I did it with my leg strength
and I could only do 100 reps.
But if my whole
body is balanced,
I should be able to do more.
She's got even more fighting
spirit than she did before!
This is the
really hard part, Sora.
You have to be in control
of your body at all times.
You can't relax,
even for an instant.
My whole body is straining.
I've only done one rep, and
I feel like I've done ten.
The special training
is moving backwards.
But I don't get why.
She can, like, barely,
like, do it now.
Miss Layla!
It's okay, I'm fine.
So I understand Sora's started
her balance training again,
is that right?
Yes Miss.
That's my Sora.
However, once you've
learned to fake a maneuver,
it's incredibly difficult
to train your body to do
the correct technique.
I have to master the technique
of instantaneously sensing
the flow of my
partner's strength.
Without that,
the "Angel's Maneuver"
will never be perfected.
Sora!
Stop!
Why?
Why are you pushing
yourself so hard?
Both you and Sophie.
Why must you be so merciless
towards yourselves?
I thought you were letting
Sora do what she wanted?
Every muscle in your body must
be burning and strained by now.
If you keep doing this,
you'll never be able
to stand on stage again.
I don't care anymore.
I refuse to give the audience
a fake "Angel's Maneuver".
Leon, are you asking me
to do a fake maneuver?
The audience won't
know the difference.
But I do, Leon.
I'll never reach my dream of
a stage without competition.
But what about my dream of
a stage with no competition.
I was fighting all along.
Fighting where
Sophie couldn't see me.
I struck down anyone
who tried to involve Sophie
in their pointless competitions.
Leon, do you think
I can become a true star?
And create a stage
with no competition?
Huh?
Yes.
I am sure you can do it, Sophie.
But when all's said and done,
I never believed in
a stage with no competition.
It's nothing but a dream.
It won't happen.
Now, you need to stop this.
I'm not surprised that you
don't believe in it, Leon.
Because nobody's
ever seen it before.
I can't imagine what
a stage without
competition is like either.
But you see that's exactly
why I wanna see it one day.
And I'm gonna do everything
in my power to make it happen.
I never knew Sophie, but I know
that she wants to see you there.
I know she wants
to watch you perform
on a stage without
competition, Leon.
Promise me, Leon?
I'm sure that
was Sophie's dream.
I know it!
You're saying that her dream
of becoming a true star,
and the promise
I made to her, you think
that was all for my sake?
Sophie knew about your battles.
She knew that you
constantly protected her.
She knew it all, Leon.
Leon, thank you.
I've changed my mind
about training.
We'll start again tomorrow.
Yes sir!
It seems like Sora is struggling
with something, doesn't it?
What's the difference between
fighting and competing?
Or the difference between
hating each other and
helping each other improve?
Everyone here knows why we
fight and tackle challenges.
Because the audience's
smiles are waiting for us.
They are, they are!
Next time on Kaleido Star:
"Our Amazing Futures".
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky.