Hey, everyone,
Kaleido Star's about to start,
so make sure your room
is brightly lit and that you're
not sitting too close to the TV.
My name is Sora Naegino.
Ever since I was a little girl
it's been my dream
to perform with Kaleido Stage.
So a few months ago I came
to the U.S. to give it a shot.
Boy, has it been an experience.
Everything is new to me,
and sometimes I'm a little lost.
But that's not going to keep me
from doing my best.
There's nothing I can't do
if I try hard enough!
Well, well, well, wouldn't you
get really depressed if someone
told you that you're the
only one who is not allowed
to do something?
This is one
of those situations.
I wonder what it is that
I can do? I wonder, I wonder.
The Amazing Distant Stage
Anna!
Oh wow Miss Anna,
you're so great!
That was horrible!
I wasn't funny at all!
Your spin trick is great, Sora.
Really?
Can all Asian people
spin like that?
What? Oh... Well...
No, but I used to do
rhythmic gymnastics...
What? What? What?!
Let me through! Let me through,
I wanna see!
Oh... So, this is it.
The show Layla and others
were practicing is Cinderella.
That's right. Even all trainees
are supposed to participate
in the show.
All of us?!
Yep. That's right.
So, good luck, everyone.
You just want to wish Sora
luck, isn't that right, Ken?
Oh, well I uh...
Cinderella...
Wow! I need to let my family
know about this quick.
My dad, mom and grandma are
huge fans of Kaleido Stage.
Since I'm their star of
hope, they'll be ecstatic
when they hear that I'll
be on the stage. So what if
I'm only going to play the
part of a pumpkin! In the end,
I'd guess you're more
the prince type, huh?
No, I'd actually rather
aim for the pumpkin.
Huh?
Oh, you know 'cause my father
is a stand-up comedian....
Oh, so that's why... Sora,
what about your family?
My family is...
They were not very enthusiastic
about you joining Kaleido Stage.
Is that right?
Yeah, a kind of... By the way,
aren't you hungry?
Let's hurry and go
to the dining hall.
Your parents, eh?
He's here again.
I'm the spirit of the stage.
Don't speak as if I'm a ghost.
So, what is the difference?
Only those who are selected for
the stage can see and hear me.
I heard ghosts are the same.
Some people can see them and
some people cannot see them.
Ugh... Are you saying that
you do not believe the things
I have telling you?
Yes.
Sora...
What's up?
Do you want to know the reason
I have presented myself to you?
You're trying to drive me mad,
so I'll screw up
you vengeful ghost.
Wrong. You're Incorrect!
I'm searching for someone
who will be able to perform
a great, legendary maneuver.
A great, legendary maneuver?
That's right. It is
an acrobatic feat that
was performed only once,
a long time ago.
For someone who cannot see me,
the maneuver would be
absolutely impossible.
What kind of maneuver?
I'm not allowed to say.
Why not?
If you're the real chosen
one, you will be possessed by
the fascination of the maneuver
as soon as you hear what it is.
Then, you'll want to force
yourself to perform that stunt.
And despite the fact that your
skills have not yet reached
that level, you would
recklessly attempt it and die.
And die?
Everybody who has tried it
without attaining the
skill level required failed to
execute the maneuver and died.
You're lying.
What?!
If what you said
is actually true,
shouldn't you be showing up
at Layla's place and not mine?
But, I said that someone
who cannot see me...
So, as I suspected, you're
trying to sabotage me. Right?
If that were my purpose,
I'd rather sabotage Layla.
She's a much bigger star. Since
my attention is on you though,
perhaps I am speaking the truth.
I hate that
I can't argue with him.
Now, please gather
around everyone!
Everyone, Kalos is
going to announce
which of you will be
cast for Cinderella.
The production of Cinderella
we will be presenting
is a masterpiece that
includes a ballroom dance scene.
So, I want all of you
to appear on the stage.
Then I will announce the roles.
First, guards for the castle.
Albert.
Yes.
Emilio.
Chris.
Yes.
Those three. That's all.
Girls in the town. Clair.
Yes.
Jean.
Prince's attendant, Anna.
Wow! It's perfect. Perfect.
Wow, I can't believe
you're going to get to
perform with Yuri.
Th...
Hum?
Th... The part
won't have gags...
No, no. No, why would it?
Ugh!
For the role of the fairy
godmother, I'll choose
some of you to practice it
first and I will select someone
from that group.
Even if you are not chosen,
you'll be appearing
in a crowd scene,
so do not let your guard down.
Now, here are the candidates
for the fairy godmother role.
Charlotte.
Yes.
Julie.
I knew it.
Mia.
Yeah!
Ah cool, you got
a role you wanted.
Wow, that's so great!
You deserve it, Mia.
Now knock 'em dead
and get that part!
Yeah, I'm gonna!
For the crowd in the ballroom
dance scene... Kevin.
Yes.
Joseph.
Miley.
I wonder... I wonder which
role I'm going to play.
Monica.
Yes!
That's all.
Huh! He didn't call my name.
I am the only one.
It must be some
kind of mistake.
Maybe, he just forgot
to call your name.
Oh, excuse me, Boss!
What?!
What is my role in Cinderella?
Well, it seems you
don't have a role.
What?
I don't have... a role?
Oh, come to think of it...
There is a role which
you can start doing as early
as tomorrow if you like.
Yes, you can be the one who
hands out toys to the children
between each show.
What? Toys?
Can you really
call that "a role"
I don't even get
to go on the stage!
If you don't like it,
then don't do it.
I'll do it!
I'll play that role!
I think your match.
Yeah, It's perfect!
Don't worry about it,
let's practice together.
Yeah, let's.
Mia, Anna...
You don't have any time for
practice with the two of them.
Because starting tomorrow,
your role will be to pass out
Kaleido Stage toys.
Okay, everyone, everyone!
Please come and get the script!
Kalos is such a creep!
Okay! I think we have no
choice, but to drop a frog
down his back or shave half
his beard while he's asleep.
Or let's go ahead and
shave a half of his eyebrows
and hair, too.
How about drawing eyes
on his sunglasses?
How about this? We'll the
sunglasses on his eyes instead?
Thank you so much
for caring about me.
But if you're worried about me,
I'm fine. I know both of you
want to hurry up and read the
script. It's really no big deal,
go on back to your rooms.
Okay.
Yeah, I guess.
Telling me that I was a person
chosen for the stage...
it must be some kind of mistake.
I told him I'd do this
dumb job because I was mad,
but everyone else is practicing
for Cinderella, while I'm...
What's this?
Oh, Layla!
So, you're the one
handing out those things?
Kalos told me to...
I see.
I was told that there were no
other rules available for me.
You still have a long way to
go -- if that's your attitude.
But...
Sora! It's almost time!
Three more minutes,
and it will be intermission.
Okay.
I'm sure the Boss has a reason
why he's giving you this role.
You know what, maybe Kalos
just doesn't like me at all.
And look at what happened
with Layla. Now I'm here
passing out toys instead
of performing on stage.
Excuse me, everyone!
Please listen to me!
Everyone, please listen!
I'm asking you guys nicely,
so please listen.
Hey, big fat clown,
outta my way!
I'm so sorry!
Mommy! My ice cream...!
Sora!
Mr. Policeman.
I'm off duty today.
So, I came to see you.
Is everything OK?
What's wrong?
HEY! You kids listen to what
my friend, Sora has to say!
What? What are all those?!
Oh, well... I wasn't
able to hand everything out
during intermission.
After you said that you would do
it, you cannot even fill a role
like handing out toys?!
I should have never made
an exception and let you join
the Kaleido Stage company!
How dare him
talking to me like that!
How does he expect me
to hand out all those toys
in such a short period of time?!
He must be having fun, asking
me to do something impossible.
Layla's up there
on the stage glowing.
And here I am off
the stage glowering...
Hah! Yah!
Sora, why don't
you give it a try?
Hum?
This is the best way to
relieve your stress, you know.
Hi - y...! Oh! Uhhh.
I would rather not....
Sora! Here, here!
You must be beat.
That was pretty rough huh?
Mm, hmm....
Hey, the food tastes
really good today, huh?
Yeah. Even the fries
are crispier than usual.
You don't need to
tiptoe around me like that.
Anyway, how was the
practice for Cinderella?
It was tough,
just as I expected.
So, what's the show like?
Well, from what I've seen, for
the last ballroom dance scene,
Layla and Yuri are supposed
to use 6 swings and then leap
from one to another
like they're dancing.
Oh, wow. So, what about
everything else that I missed?
It appears that you have neither
the desire nor motivation
to do anything.
Don't bother
telling me my fortune;
as you see it's a no brainer.
But, you see Sora Naegino
this is also the card
that governs creation. The road
is blocked. If you want what is
up along that road, you
have to create your own road.
I have no clue what
you're talking about.
What do you mean by
"my own road?" Oh, yeah!
Is this okay?
Thanks Ken.
Are you really going to
do it in a clown costume?
Yup. If I cannot
appear on the stage,
I should turn the audience seats
into my own special stage.
Turn the audience
seats into your stage?
You bet!
The way you always have
this positive attitude is...
great, you know?
Sheesh, Ken, get going already.
Oh, sorry!
All right, I'm set!
Hello, everyone! Are you
enjoying Kaleido Stage?
Yeah!
Now, my friends, everyone
who wants a glow light,
gather around!
Hurry up and grab one,
the show is about to begin!
Oh yeah!
One for you. And one
for you. And one for you.
And one for you. And one
And one for you.
I did it! I finished handing
everything out today. Hum?
You obviously have
no understanding of what
running a show is all about.
Oh, are you talking
about this costume?
It has nothing to do
with costumes.
Why don't you think
seriously what your role is!
What's wrong?! I don't
understand what you mean.
Sora...
What?
Because of what you did,
the next show was delayed
by more than 10 minutes.
What?
You put on a pretty
flashy performance,
so it took a really long time
to calm down the audience.
Oh...
And... You made the kids
come up to get the lights.
Right? Some kids couldn't find
their way back to their seats
and some of them were in such
a hurry that tripped and fell.
I... I... just.
Sora...
I was only thinking about
getting attention for myself.
All I could think of was
to get people to say that
I was amazing. I wasn't thinking
at all about the progression
of the show. I don't blame
Kalos for being mad at me.
Oh, so, it's you.
Uh, Yuri.
I do not really want to see
a clown crying you know.
Even if your own heart is
crying, isn't it the job
of the clown to make
other people happy, Sora?
Sora!
What are you doing
dressed like that, Ken?
I will help you
to hand out the lights.
Thank you.
Ah no, anything for you, Sora.
But I'll be fine,
because I finally understand
what the role that I've been
given is. And I can do it.
Huh?
A clown's job
is making people happy.
Sora, what are you doing?
Mom look!
Uh-uhn?
See that clown over there
it hasn't moved at all
since we came in.
Is she alive?
Hey. It looks funny.
Hey hey you? Are you a doll?
I can't believe she's
performing in the lobby...
The show has already started.
But I can still play my role
to the fullest whether
I am on the stage or not.
Oh, that is the clown
I saw in the lobby.
Mom, she wasn't
a doll after all.
Now, I am here to give
everyone a magic wand!
Everyone, use your powers to
fill the night sky with stars,
okay?!
Okay!
I don't have
a leading role or anything,
if I can bring everyone just
a little enjoyment in my role
as a supporting character,
then I'm doing my best.
Sora, you did it.
No, I've not finished it yet.
I'm starting to understand. All
roles exist for the audience
so that we can bring them a
smile. That is Kaleido Stage.
Layla!
Oh! Hi there... What is it?
Um...
What? Me? You're sure
you want me to do it?
A-An autograph... let me
think... how should I write it?
Here.
Thank you.
No, not at all. I'm the one
who should be thanking you.
Tim, Come, on now!
Okay.
Bye.
Sora, you did a good job.
I signed my first autographed!
It would be nice
if the boy could
cherish your autograph forever.
Yeah.
Kalos.
Hum?
I wonder what could you possibly
be expecting out of such a girl?
Hum... Hum...
What do you think?
Your autograph is terrible.
What? Really?
First of all, there are
several other things that you
should to practice before
you practice your penmanship.
Wouldn't you agree Sora?
Uh... Of course, you're right.
But I feel like I understand now
what you were trying
to tell me earlier, Fool.
Creating my own road means
creating my own role.
And waiting for me
up that road is...
is the smile on the
faces of the audience.
Are you thanking me?
Yeah, I guess so...
Then, keep that
thought in your heart.
And now it's time
for you to go to bed.
Hey! What are you doing? Stop
blindfolding me! Let me down.
Hey, Sora!
How ungrateful!
I don't want any of you
pathetic losers practicing
on the trampoline.
And so, the three of us
have ended up in Mia's role
as the fairy godmother,
but Marion is...
Marion started crying,
and said she doesn't want us
to get up on the trampoline.
I heard that Marion's deceased
mother used to be a member
of the trampoline cast.
Maybe, I'm not supposed
to appear on the stage yet.
Maybe, just maybe,
maybe, maybe...
Next time, on Kaleido Star
"Try hard, and you'll
get an amazing chance."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...