Hello, everyone,
Kaleido Star is about to start.
Please make sure the
room is brightly lit
and that you're not sitting
too close to the TV, okay?
Well, well, well...
Doesn't it make you nervous
sometimes when you go someplace
you've never been before?
A place where
everything seems foreign,
and you don't know what to do?
A place where everyone gets mad
at you just because you're new?!
I can't take it anymore! Okay,
just breathe, just breathe...
Good show, everybody!
Oh! Great it's vacation time!
I almost don't know what to do
with a full week of free time.
What do you think about
taking a trip someplace?
Man you've got a lot of energy.
I just wanna sit on the beach.
Oh, that sounds nice...
The beach?
Not me, I wanna go someplace
I've never even heard of before
and then cut loose!
And I'll--
Sora.
Uh? What is it, Boss?
Here you go.
Is this an airline ticket?
Oh my gosh, Boss, are you
rewarding all my hard work
by giving me a trip
someplace exotic?
Thank you, thank you!
That's great!
Looks like you got your wish.
It's work.
A dirty trick...
On the bright side,
at least you get to travel.
My friend Mr. Pack runs
a circus, and he's asked
to have you come
as a guest performer.
Stay calm... oh I don't
know if I can do this...
This card foretells
an ordeal. A sacrifice.
'Mysterious Amazing Circus.'
Kalos wanted you to have a
manager with you on this trip.
So that's why I'm here.
Right. Oh, Ken, I'm so glad I'll
have somebody I know with me!
Wow. Life can be
pretty good sometimes.
The place we're going
is called Theatrical Camp.
Theatrical Camp?
It's a mobile circus.
And they specialize in different
things than Kaleido Stage,
like knife-throwing,
fire-breathing, whip tricks
and keg juggling.
I see... So, should I start
practicing fire breathing?
I don't think so...
Strangers!
Ken...
Hey. Don't worry, I'll find out
where we're supposed to be.
This way.
We've been expecting you.
Pleased to meet you,
Miss Naegino.
Theatrical Camp welcomes you.
Wow, she's really
breathing fire!
Here you go!
Excuse me!
It's like the audience
is part of the show.
Hey, no fair, Milo!
I didn't do anything!
Why'd you eat that?
You knew it was mine!
Tank, how many times
do I have to tell you?
Get out of my ring when
you're done with your kegs!
But the kids were so happy...
Don't do it again!
Whatever you say...
Excuse me...
Don't look at me like that.
Wait!
I didn't do it!
Then why are you running?
Because you're chasing me!
Hello?!
I see you've all met our guest.
This is Miss Sora Naegino.
Kalos from Kaleido Stage sent
me. It's nice to meet you all.
Uh, and I'm Sora's
manager. Ken Robbins.
Kaleido Stage, huh?
Enjoy everyone!
I don't like to brag, but
today's stew is delicious!
Yay! Food!
As for tomorrow's performance,
I was thinking we'd do
that piece we
haven't done in a while.
Since we have a guest and all.
Sora, I'd like for you
to be the lead, a princess.
The lead role?!
Yes.
Yeah!
And in tomorrow's performance?
I don't know if
I can do it, Mr. Pack...
She's not even gonna try.
Maybe she just flat-out
isn't good enough.
Well, I guess I can
give it my best shot.
Oh, what's the use?
It's impossible.
The story itself
is very simple.
You'll be playing
a princess who has to rescue
her little twin sisters
from an evil sorceress.
Okay.
Dominique, the twins just
threw their carrots away again.
So I guess that means
you guys need a refill. Eat up.
Pamela, you'll be
playing the sorceress.
Right.
Tank, you'll be the glutton
with super-human strength.
I gotcha.
The princess will fight against
a knife-wielding monster
before making her way
to the witch's lair.
Uh, Pack. You've
forgotten my part.
Ah yes, Dio. Your character
is the princess's only ally.
They work together
to rescue the twins,
falling in love along the way.
A happy ending, no?
Nice to meet you.
Oh! It's nice to meet you, too!
The love story part
sounds unnecessary to me...
There there.
Could you give him
some milk please?
Sure.
Chocolate.
Eclair.
Radio station.
Noodle.
Elephant.
This script
talks about the story,
but doesn't have any
information on my routines.
I wonder what I'll be doing.
At any rate, I guess I'd better
get some sleep before tomorrow.
You're cheating!
Me cheating, you're
the one who's cheating,
you're always cheating!
I can't sleep!
Ken?
Sora. Did you come out
to look at the stars?
They're beautiful. Ken?
Yeah?
Thank you for being so great.
For what now?
I mean, every time I'm
not sure I can do something,
you're always there
helping me and cheering me on.
Without you, I never would
have found my Little Mermaid.
And I never would have
made it through the audition
for Arabian Nights.
Uh, I don't
know about that, Sora.
You succeeded
because you worked hard.
I don't think that's true.
Of course it is.
You're a hard worker.
Sometimes I think
you work too hard,
and you're going places where
I won't be able to follow you.
Huh?
You must be tired. Maybe you
should try to go get some sleep.
Well... it's kinda
noisy in there...
Really?
But you're right, I should
probably get back inside.
Yeah, I guess so.
You never know,
maybe they've quieted down.
See you in the morning!
Okay.
That baby cried all night long.
Really? I couldn't hear
anything over Tank's snoring.
There's nobody here.
The men aren't
in their quarters, either.
Then what are we
going to do about rehearsal?
Oh, there's not going to be
any rehearsal, sweetie.
You-- you're kidding, right?
Afraid not. These folks
just don't go in for that.
Uh. You don't happen
to know where they went?
Oh, baby,
this is their free time.
They're scattered to the winds.
It's coming
from the stage area.
It's Dio!
I'm so glad! I thought everybody
had gone off and left me.
I'll bet everyone else
is out sightseeing. Huh.
I guess I should probably
get out of here and go do
some of that myself.
See ya later.
Oh, wait a minute!
You mean you guys
really don't rehearse at all?!
I -- I've never performed
without a rehearsal!
That's too bad.
Look, Sora, is it okay if I give
you a little piece of advice?
Yes.
When you watched the show
yesterday I'm sure you saw
that each member of the troupe
has their own specialty.
The story's just there so we
can show off what we do best.
If you just pay attention
to the audience's reaction
you'll know what to do.
Follow the
audience's reaction...
Right. Just show them what
they wanna see. Just relax.
Thanks for the advice, Dio.
Show what I do best...
Princess, if you ever want to
see your little sisters again,
come to my castle and
we'll see who is stronger!
Help us!
Uh... I wonder if that
was my cue. Should I go on?
I can't tell...
It's you! Go!
You're the leading lady.
You've got to act like it!
Mila, Milo, where have you run
off to? I hope that the witch--
I wasn't finished
with my line...
Sora...
Looks like everything's
going smoothly.
What do you mean?
Hey! What are
you doi--?! Stop it!
Oh, there's my beer kegs!
It's high time we see
just how brave this princess is!
Now stay still, okay?
If you're looking for me,
I'm right here, Princess!
I've got to show them
what I can do.
Here I go.
You're nothing.
You should all be ashamed
of yourselves, Mr. Pack.
If this is how Sora's
going to be treated,
there's no way I'm going to let
her appear on your stage again.
Well, if that's how Sora
feels there's
nothing I can do about it.
They think putting someone
in danger's entertainment.
I just don't
understand these people.
If you want to leave
I'll explain everything
to Kalos for you.
I don't care if they
make fun of my mistakes.
But that's not
what they were doing.
They were making fun of me
because I'm an outsider.
Yesterday's performance
I thought it was amazing how
the audience and cast seemed
to be working together
to make the show.
But today it seemed like
everyone was just trying
to humiliate me.
I mean, they didn't
even let me perform.
Is this about Pamela?
How did you know?
It was awful what
she did to you up there.
But did you happen to
notice what she was doing
before you grabbed the trapeze?
I know you didn't mean to,
Sora, but you stole
her biggest moment.
That's why...?
I see. Dio, thanks
so much for telling me.
Oh, go to sleep already.
What do you want?
I'm sorry I ruined
your big moment.
I'll bet you're ready to go
running back home after today.
This isn't like Kaleido Stage,
where all you have to do is
follow a script to get applause.
A monkey could do that.
You don't know anything
about Kaleido Stage.
And I'm not about
to leave here.
Really?
As long as I'm
performing with your troupe,
I expect you to treat me
as a member of your company.
That means when I jump
tomorrow you're gonna catch me.
If I feel like it.
Look at this, it's a fool.
You!
It's just as I'd feared:
you've been too tossed around
by the storms of life
to even say hello.
What the heck
are you doing here?
Oh. I stay locked away in your
suitcase for days just because
I know you're going to need
my expert guidance and this
is the kind of
thanks I get? Hm?
I'm glad you're here.
You've got hands
like a dock worker.
Maybe you're in
the wrong line of work.
I, uh thought I saw a roach.
First, we should talk about
the performance space, I guess.
Right.
They want to fit as many seats
as they can into the tent.
So the stage is gonna be small.
And the audience is going to be
a lot closer to the performers
here than they would be
at Kaleido Stage.
That means they can see
your facial expressions
when you're performing.
You're right.
So doing my routines from
Kaleido Stage won't impress
the audiences here.
I have to pay attention to
what everyone else is doing
when they perform and follow
the audience's response.
Unless I can do that,
they'll never treat me
like one of the company.
Princess, if you ever want to
see your little sisters again,
come to my castle and
we'll see who is stronger!
Help us!
You're on!
Right!
Mila, Milo? Where did
you two wander off to?
Did the witch kidnap them?
I'm the only one
who can rescue them!
Don't be afraid,
little sisters.
I'll find you! Huh?
What did I do wrong?
Yeah!
Hey, quit it!
I know!
Oh! My kegs!
Thank you, thank you!
Maybe I can do this after all.
Ready?
That's a smaller target
than I'm used to...
Yeah!
Not too shabby.
If you're looking for me,
I'm right here, Princess!
I'll show you what it takes to
be a leading lady around here.
No that's too high!
Amazing...
You're incredible, Pamela.
I've never seen anyone jump
that high on the swings before.
I'm glad you caught me
on a good day--
I can only pull it off
one in every five tries.
But I didn't want you
to outdo me up there.
There's no way I could...
Sora, Theatrical Camp isn't
about doing difficult maneuvers,
it's about performing.
The most important thing
is to take care of yourself
so you can keep
showing up on stage.
Working here's so
different from Kaleido Stage.
I don't know how you guys
do it day after day,
creating a new show every
time for each audience.
That's what I thought, too,
when I first came here
from Kaleido Stage.
But now I really like
the way we do things here.
I'm not afraid
to try new things.
That is nice, I guess...
You're a risk-taker,
too, aren't you?
Well, I guess
you could say that.
You know, I think you're
just the kind of performer
that Kaleido Stage
needs right now, Sora.
Thanks.
It looks like you'll be going
back sooner than I expected.
Yes. Milo twisted an ankle
during the performance today.
I would rather cancel
all the rest of the shows
than have someone perform
while they're injured.
What kind of trees are those?
They're olives.
Pack plants olive trees wherever
we camp. It's kind of a hobby.
Did you know that olives are
a symbol of peace because they
can grow back even after they've
been burned to the ground?
I think that's why I like them.
Well, that and they're essential
for a good salad.
She's really very charming.
I've seen a lot of people play
that princess, including Pamela,
but I've never seen anyone bring
the kind of talent and energy
to it that Sora did today.
I think she'll be better
than anyone we've ever seen
if she just gets the
right kind of guidance.
Right.
Don't worry, I'll make sure she
gets all the help she needs.
Will you come see me perform
at Kaleido Stage sometime?
If I feel like it.
Hey, that's not very nice...
He told me he
doesn't need me anymore.
Oh no! It looks like Sarah
might be leaving Kaleido Stage!
And not only that...
They've secretly been
in love for ten years!
It's a love triangle!
How romantic!
Ugh, everything
is so complicated!
But I can't just let
her leave! Can I? Can I?
Join us next time for
'The Diva's Amazing Love.'
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...