Everyone, Kaleido Star is
about to start, so make sure
that your room is brightly lit
and that you're not sitting
too close to your TV.
Well, well, well.
Do you know what you want
to be when you grow up?
A school teacher? A doctor?
There are so many choices
it's hard to decide!
And sometimes, once you decide,
it can be even harder
to stick with your dream.
But it's really worth it,
so don't ever give up, 'cause
I know you'll do great.
Just keep trying, keep trying!
'An Amazing Sinister Rumor.'
And now, the moment you've all
been waiting for: my homepage!
It's adorable!
Hold on a sec: you've got a
link on the Kaleido Stage site?
Don't worry. I already asked the
Boss, and he said it was okay.
It's amazing!
There's still a whole lot of
stuff I'd like to do with it
before I'm finished.
So far Anna's the only one I've
got pictures of in the Gallery.
Hey, where did you get those?
I took them. You're really
photogenic when you're trying
to come up with a good gag.
Are you going to put pictures
of everyone in there?
Well, I was planning on it,
but maybe not...
Why not?
Because lately it seems like
someone different has been
quitting every day.
What?
Didn't you know about this?
Last week, three people
quit at the same time.
It's too much work to put
pictures of people on the site
if I don't know who's
staying and who's going.
So, that's why I've decided I'm
going to my channel energies
and start writing a series
of original stories.
What kind of stories?
Oh, all kinds. Love stories,
horror stories,
history stories...
How about something funny?
Nope, not interested.
Sora? Someone's here to see you.
Coming!
I think she's someone
you know from Japan.
She's Japanese?
I wonder who it could be?
She said she'd wait
for you in the lobby.
Great. Thanks, Ken!
I wonder if it's someone from
the rhythmic gymnastics club...
Now, where is...?
Excuse me...
You sure took your time.
I was starting to
get tired of waiting.
Manami?!
What's wrong?
It doesn't bother you that
I came to visit, does it?
No, no. I'm just
surprised to see you here.
I want to catch up, but I'm
sick of standing in this lobby,
so what do you say
we get some coffee?
I mean, you can get out of here
until the evening
performance, right?
And Sora?
I won't be seen in public
with you if you wear that.
Huh? I'm still in costume!
Be right back...
So, what are you doing
in Cape Mary, Manami?
I'm part of a student-exchange
program, so I'll be studying
in Boston for three months.
Wow. Well, you always
were really good in school.
You could've been, too,
if you ever took
the time to study, Sora.
Oh, I don't think
I could ever be as smart
as you are if I tried.
Well, maybe that's because
you wasted your time going
to English conversation school
while everyone who actually
wanted to succeed
went to cram school.
Yeah, I think you've mentioned
that a couple times before.
I know. That's why
I was so surprised today.
Well you know I really
never thought that
I'd see you playing the lead.
When you said you were
coming here to be a star
of Kaleido Stage, I thought
you'd lost your mind.
I never thought you'd
actually pull it off.
Well, I haven't yet,
I mean, I've still got
a long way to go--
I was just lucky they needed
a second female lead this
time so Layla and I could--
So that's why.
Do you ever regret it?
Coming here's the
best thing I've ever done.
So I don't regret being here,
but I really would have
regretted staying in Japan.
Is something wrong, Manami?
What do you mean?
It's like you're having a hard
time deciding what to do.
You've always seemed so sure
of yourself, but now...
You can be
really rude sometimes.
Don't treat me like a moron
just because you're happy.
I didn't mean it
to sound that way, honestly.
Ugh, stop groveling. Besides,
you have to be getting back.
This time I figured I'd just
wait for you backstage after
you finish with the show, okay?
Oh, you're going
to see the show again?
Of course not.
I'm coming back because I'm
staying in your room tonight.
I don't have
a hotel reservation.
Oh really...?
And this is where
our dressing rooms are.
Oh no, it wouldn't be
fair to you -- I can't even
hold you in my arms!
Please, it doesn't matter to
me that you're just a ghost.
I don't ever want
to live without you.
What are you guys doing?
Hey, Sora!
Oh and who's our visitor?
This is Manami,
a friend from home.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
When you came in we were
acting out one of the stories
Mia has posted on her website.
You want us to give you a part?
What? Me?
Yeah! And I've got the
perfect role for you, too.
What is it?
The mysterious comic crazy-girl.
The mysterious... what, now?
Aww, that sounds like
the best part...
She'll be perfect!
Good choice, Mia.
Can't I try another part?
My lines are embarrassing...
Oh, teenage girls are going
to think you're adorable.
That's just what I said!
Great show you guys!
Sora, do you have a minute?
Sure.
Did I see you holding
your back at curtain call?
Uh no, I--
You need to tell me the truth.
If your body's hurting,
I need to know it.
I--
Look, Sora, it's
perfectly understandable.
Your body isn't as trained as
Layla's is, but you're doing
the same performance she is
day after day and it's bound
to take its toll.
You're right...
So... I was thinking maybe
I could be your trainer.
My trainer?
I-- I mean if you want me to.
I already got permission
from Kalos, just in case.
I figured the first thing
we'd do is look at your diet.
See if you're eating things
that can actually help you.
And then, well, we can
figure out the rest as we go.
That would be great-- if
it's not too much trouble...
Don't be silly,
it's no trouble at all!
I guess it makes sense.
My body's been doing
a lot more lately,
but I haven't changed anything
about my lifestyle...
Hey, did you hear the latest?
Karen's gonna be leaving, too.
Then I wonder if
the rumors are true...?
They have to be.
There's a headhunter
around here somewhere.
Kaleido Stage won't be able
to survive much longer
if this keeps up.
Whaddaya want?
Sorry. I couldn't
help overhearing...
Personally, I think everyone's
quitting because of you, Sora.
And who could blame them?
I mean, you're totally green and
you're getting all the leads?
Hey, where did Manami go?
I don't know. She wasn't
here when we got off stage.
Hey I just heard a rumor that
people are leaving the cast
because I'm playing
a leading role.
Do you think that's true?
That's totally ridiculous, Sora.
If you heard that
from Julie and Charlotte,
you know you can't take
anything they say seriously.
I know...
There are a lot of rumors
flying around, though.
I heard there was going
to be a new circus company.
Competing against Kaleido Stage?
Not only that,
they're taking our cast!
Oh, whatever.
As long as we have Layla,
Sora and Yuri we'll be fine.
She has so many things
to deal with. Sora?
Oh, Manami, you're still here!
What, you want me to leave?
Uh? Oh no, of course I don't!
One, two. One, two. One, two.
Great, now try it more slowly.
I've got to
build up more muscle.
So I can keep up with Layla.
Layla may be stronger on stage,
but is her boyfriend
as cute as yours?
What are you talking about?
Are you talking about Ken,
because he's not my boyfriend.
Not at all!
Uh... I left that
protein shake I made for you
in the refrigerator.
You're supposed to drink it
right after a workout.
Helps you recover
faster. I'll go get it.
You're the best, Ken, thanks!
I think he was about to cry.
No way...
What a long day. Hey, Manami?
Do you want to take a bath?
Sure. What are you doing?
Uh arm exercises. Sort of
as a cool-down, you know?
But, I haven't
done anything! Yet.
Sora, it looks like it's been
a long time since
you've had your hair cut.
Come to think of it
it has been a while heh.
Then I guess you need me
to cut it for you.
It's funny, I remember when
we were little kids you
always wanted to play salon.
You always made me
be the customer...
I made you?
I mean 'let me.'
Well, it looks like you've found
the place where you belong,
Kaleido Stage seems
like it's perfect for you.
You know, I've been watching
you all day long, Sora.
When we were at the
restaurant earlier you seemed
to have everything under
control, but I wanted to see
if you were really
as happy as you seemed.
Were you worried
about me, Manami?
Not really.
Actually, I I was hoping that
you'd gotten here and realized
you'd made a terrible
mistake with your life.
What?
Yes. Yes, everything
is going smoothly.
Huh?
After I watch your
show one last time,
I'm catching an evening
flight to Boston. Manami.
Manami...
One, two. One, two. One, two.
Quietly, folks. Like a feather
not like an elephant...
Come on now, give it
your best! One, two...
So, the girl who was here...
She's leaving for Boston
after the show tonight.
She was one of
your friends, right?
Right.
But you always seem
so nervous around her.
Manami can be a
little intimidating...
Miss Sora Naegino!
What makes you think
that you're allowed to
chitchat in my class?!
Do you think you're not going
to be punished just because
you're playing a starring role?
Well, you've got
another thing coming!
Uh Yuri!
Excuse me,
I need to borrow Sora.
If that's all right
with you, of course.
Ah, certainly. You can
have anything you want,
all you have to do is ask.
Thank you, you're too kind.
How exciting! Yuri
wants to talk to me!
I-- I'm so sorry!
Don't be so nervous, Sora.
How could I not be nervous?
I'm having lunch with
Kaleido Stage's biggest star,
someone I've been admiring
since I was a little kid!
It's good to hear that.
Because I was going to ask
you to come away with me.
What?! What do
you mean by that?
I want you to come
work for me, Sora,
after you quit Kaleido Stage.
What did you just say?
I will be withdrawing from
Kalos's company as of today.
I'm going to
create a new circus.
I want you to be a part of it.
But, Yuri...
You'll be the star of my show.
Not Layla, not anyone else.
You're not serious.
You'd never leave the company,
right? You're just testing me.
This isn't just some kind
of trick. Kaleido Stage isn't
the perfect place
you've made it out to be.
You'll find out sooner
or later. Like I did.
I'm not asking you
to decide right now,
but I will need your answer
in the next few days.
We're in trouble.
Twenty-five people turned
in their resignations today.
What should we do
about the shows?
We've got no choice
but to cancel.
I guess you're right
but how can we keep
everyone else from leaving?
I can't believe this...
Sora. It's awful!
All our performances are
canceled indefinitely.
What? Canceled?
I don't believe it...
Twenty-five more people
turned in their notice;
tonight's their
last performance.
Even Yuri and a few of
the directors are leaving.
The company's finished.
It can't be...
I will be withdrawing from
Kalos's company as of today.
I'm going to
create a new circus.
I want you to be a part of it.
So Yuri wasn't just
testing me after all...
I've done it!
I've beaten Kalos!
This could be the last show.
Kaleido Stage...
is it finished?
I'm sorry about
what happened earlier.
Oh don't worry about it.
The audience couldn't
have been happier.
Yuri approached you about
leaving today, didn't he?
Yes.
What did you say?
No.
I see...
Someone also
approached my father
about buying
Kaleido Stage outright.
Supposedly a businessman
from Las Vegas.
I've known for a long time
that Yuri was up to something,
but I didn't know what.
I just I wish he would've
talked to me about this,
then maybe I could've
made him reconsider.
What'll they do with the ship?
It doesn't look like we'll
be using it any time soon.
I know. If only we
hadn't lost so many people.
But I guess there'd be no way
to replace Yuri. I have to go.
Good night, Layla.
Thanks for everything.
See you around, Kalos.
Are you satisfied?
Yes. Just seeing that
look on your face has made
all of this worthwhile.
Sora?
I saw you make
a mistake out there.
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry, you didn't
see the best show today...
I... Actually,
I came here to apologize.
I said something really
kind of mean last night,
I said I was hoping you realized
it was a mistake to come here.
If that's what made you
lose your focus today--
Oh, it wasn't that.
I was thinking about something
completely different.
You see, Kaleido Stage is going
through a really rough time
right now.
Performances are going to
be canceled indefinitely.
And just when
I'd gotten my first lead
in a show opposite Layla...
So, is Kaleido Stage
shutting down for good?
I don't know.
If they do close it down,
would you still not have
any regrets about
leaving Japan to come here?
No. I'd still be glad.
Why?
Because I had to come,
Manami, this is my dream.
You know, I always thought you
were dumb... But I envy you.
I always wanted
to be a hairdresser.
Really?
Yeah. But I was always good
in school so my parents expected
me to do something better.
Uh...
That's why I had to
come to the U.S. to study,
I had to get as far away
from Japan as I could.
I know my parents mean well,
but it just got too
stifling after a while.
I think that's wonderful. You'll
be an awesome hairdresser.
You really are dumb.
Things aren't that simple.
I can't disappoint
my family like that.
Oh. Right...
I can't just do what
I want like you can, Sora.
Do you even know
why I came here?
I came to see you admit that
you'd made a terrible mistake.
I'll bet you think that's
the most pathetic thing
you've ever heard, right.
No, I think I need
another haircut.
I want to be your salon's
very first customer, Manami.
I'll support you no matter
what kind of career you choose,
but choose one that makes
you happy, all right?
I'm gonna stay at Kaleido
Stage as long as I can.
I can spend my time worrying
about it and hoping it doesn't
close down or I can decide
this is where I wanna be and
I'm gonna make it work. Right?
I guess you're a little
smarter than I gave you
credit for, Sora.
Maybe just a little bit.
Well, I've gotta go.
It was good seeing you again.
Yeah.
See ya. Oh, and you make sure
to take care of yourself
out here, understood?
Yeah sure.
So what do you think of it,
Boss? Isn't her story good?
I knew he'd hate it, Sora!
This is so embarrassing!
No.
You see? He hates it.
But, Boss, we need
a new show to do.
And Mia's script would be the
perfect production for a company
as small as ours is now.
One week.
Have it ready to go in front
of an audience by
a week from today.
Yes, sir!
This show's going to be better
than Shakespeare, I know it!
Not only does Mia get
to write our next show,
she has to direct it as well!
Until Yuri stops swooping in and
trying to take our best people,
things are gonna be
pretty weird around here.
Layla thinks Kalos is crazy
for letting us try this,
but I know Mia can do it.
I know it, I know it!
Join us next time for
'Fire It Up! Amazing Mia.'
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...