Hey, everyone,
Kaleido Star's about to start,
so make sure your room
is brightly lit and that you're
not sitting too close to the TV.
My name is Sora Naegino.
Ever since I was a little girl
it's been my dream
to perform with Kaleido Stage.
So a few months ago I came
to the U.S. to give it a shot.
Boy, has it been an experience.
Everything is new to me,
and sometimes I'm a little lost.
But that's not going to keep me
from doing my best.
There's nothing I can't do
if I work hard!
Having friends
makes life so much easier.
I mean, whenever I have
a bad day, all I have to do
is tell Anna and Mia
about it and I feel better.
We don't always see eye to eye,
but we're always there for each
other, and we're always helping
each other be better performers.
With their help,
I just know I'll be a star
of Kaleido Stage someday!
The sting of humiliation,
the thrill of pursuit,
and the bliss of new love.
Kaleido Stage presents
'Cinderella.' Starring
Layla Hamilton in the title role
and Yuri Killian as her prince.
In the supporting roles,
we proudly present the
debut performances of our
newest troupe members.
Come experience all the romance,
the wonder, the danger
of this classic story...
Anna's gonna be really great
as the Prince's Attendant.
And Mia! She won the role of
the Fairy Godmother after some
really tough competition. I
can't wait to see them perform.
But I wish I had been cast, too.
So you're jealous, huh?
Well I guess I--
What are you doing back here?
Audience members aren't allowed
to come back stage, little girl.
And you're not allowed on stage.
Well I wouldn't say
that I'm not allowed.
I mean, I've been
on the stage before.
You must've been terrible.
Well it wasn't the best
performance but I was
just starting out. I mean, for
being my very first performance
it actually went pretty--
What a loser.
Who was that kid anyway?
'Try Hard and You'll Get
an Amazing Chance!'
Wow.
It looks like Mia's
gonna be awesome.
I know...
Come on, Mia, jump higher.
Okay.
Too slow.
Right.
Not high enough.
You've got to make the
audience want to watch you.
Okay.
They've been
doing this all morning.
Haven't even taken a break.
What?
You're kidding!
They must be exhausted.
I'm sorry.
Layla?
There's no point in doing it
again. You're not concentrating.
I'll get it right
this time, I swear...
Don't bother. This if
a very important scene, Mia.
If you aren't up to it, then
we'll find someone else who is.
Wha--?
This routine is the
climax of the first act.
If the Fairy Godmother's not
perfect we might as well cancel.
Please, Layla! Give me another
chance, please! I can do this,
I know I can! Layla?
What did I tell you?
I knew she'd never
be able to pull it off.
They should've cast me
for it in the first place.
So are they gonna
cancel the performance?
They'll have to if
that doesn't get any better.
Mia!
Are you all right?
You should take a break
before you hurt yourself.
Leave me alone.
You can't nail that routine if
you don't take care of yourself.
Go away. I have
to keep practicing.
Why bother? It's not
like you're ever gonna
get better at it
anyway. You stink.
It's you again.
You know this kid?
Marion! Don't interrupt
practice. Get back over here.
Okay.
Cute kid.
Yeah, right.
Who is she?
Her name is Marion.
She's the daughter of Jean,
one of our carpenters.
That's why she was backstage...
Is she always that sweet?
A few years ago, her mother was
the star of our trampoline act.
So she really knows a lot
about performing on it.
I guess she can be
kind of critical when
she sees someone who's
not... well... not quite up
to her standards.
So, who's her mother?
Uh, you've never met her.
She died a while ago.
Collapsed one day after
she came off the stage.
Oh that's awful.
Yeah. Must've been rough.
It was.
Mia...?
I'm fine. I'm
going back to work.
You know, Mia's grandmother
isn't doing too well.
She's having surgery
on our opening day.
Really? So, was Layla right
about Mia not being able
to concentrate?
I mean, if she's worried abou--
No, uh uh, I think
she's concentrating too hard.
What?
Mia's grandmother has always
been her biggest supporter,
and I know that Mia
doesn't want to let her down.
When they found out that
our opening and her surgery
were on the same day,
they made a pact.
They both agreed
to do their best.
So that's why she's pushing
herself so hard in practice.
Right. But the thing
about Mia is...
she loses her cool
when she tries too hard.
I'm so sorry, Grandma.
But... I may not be able to
keep up my end of the bargain.
Make Fairy Godmother
a three-person role?
How about it?
You're joking.
I think it sounds interesting.
Wouldn't that make it
more difficult?
It would, but I know Anna,
Sora and I would do a great job.
You want...?
Really?
Come again?
That's right, I'd be
performing with Anna and Sora.
What?! We can't do that!
You don't want to?
Uh, that's not the point.
It doesn't matter anyway.
Kalos would never authorize
this kind of casting change.
Go ahead.
It's a rather
interesting idea,
and I'm curious to see
what you girls will do with it.
I'll make sure the director
and Layla are okay with it.
You mean it's all right
with you that I appear on stage?
That depends on the level
of your performance.
I will give you
three days ladies.
If I do not like what I see
after that I'm following
Layla's suggestion and
canceling all the performances.
Understood?
Yes! Thank you so much, boss.
Yeah!
Yay!
I can't believe he's
letting us perform together.
Yeah, but now we have to
create the coolest trick ever.
Thanks a lot, guys.
No, thank you; without you
I wouldn't be on stage.
Sora?
Are you okay?
I'm starting to have fun
handing out the toys.
But to be on stage is--
well, that's the whole reason
why I came here isn't it?
And now thanks to you guys I
might just get another chance!
So how 'bout we get
this party started?
That's right,
let's get you on stage.
Thanks, guys.
And then this is the climax.
We all jump towards the
center and we hand off wands.
That's the ninth routine
where we've all ended up
with massive head injuries.
Well look on the bright side,
at least the three of us
are only getting maimed
in a simulation.
Don't worry, guys,
I'll come up with something.
It's gotta be
spectacular, though,
or else they're gonna cancel.
What comes to mind
when you think 'Cinderella?'
The glass slippers.
What comes to mind for you?
The handsome pumpkin prince.
That's not part of the story.
Well it should be.
That's it!
That is it!
You're not talking about
the pumpkin prince, are you?
Oh, let me play that role!
No.
What? Why?
Uh, I don't know
what you're talking about.
But check this out:
we'll put some kind
of device in our wands
so that when we jump out
we spread a triangle of fabric.
And then when we jump up... See?
A pumpkin! What do you think?
Wow.
That's a pretty cool trick.
It's gonna be tough, though.
I mean, if we don't jump
to exactly the right height
at exactly the right time, it's
not gonna look like a pumpkin.
I know. But I'm not done yet.
Once we make the pumpkin,
I was thinking Cinderella
could appear inside it.
That is so cool.
You really think we'll be
able to put all that together
in three days?
We'll just have
to get practicing.
I think I'll call it
'The Triple Illusion.'
The Triple Illusion?
'Cause there are three of us.
Good name.
Then it's settled. Intensive
training for the Triple Illusion
starts first thing tomorrow.
This is gonna be great.
Yeah!
I've got to work hard.
Mia put her neck on the
line to get me this chance.
I'm not gonna let her down!
What's the problem, little one?
What the heck
are you doing in my bed?
What, there's not
enough room? Lie down.
No way.
Suit yourself. I was
just offering to help you...
Help me, how?
Just a bit of friendly advice:
don't partner up
with those two girls.
But why?
The level of talent
is too different.
I know I stink.
But I'll never get better
unless I work with good people.
Sora, you're not the problem.
Hey.
Turn off the light, will you?
I've gotta get some sleep.
The inverted star.
It foretells failure.
Will you just
turn off the light!
Oh fine.
I'm sorry.
I messed it up again.
Quit apologizing.
All of us were off.
I just can't catch it.
I mean I feel like I keep making
the same mistake over and over.
Sorry.
Stop taking responsibility,
Sora, the three of us
just weren't synchronized.
We're just not working
as a team yet.
Back me up here.
Mia?
If you don't think I can do this
routine, it's okay just tell m--
I never said you couldn't do it.
My timing was messed up,
so it's just as much
my fault as anyone else's.
No, it's my fault.
For having this stupid idea
in the first place.
You people are pathetic.
No-talent losers like you
have no business
being on that trampoline.
I mean, do you even know
how stupid you sound?
'It's my fault.'
'No, it's my fault.'
Back off, kid. This isn't
any of your business.
Get out of here!
You're not fit...
you're not fit... any of you
to use the same trampoline
as my mother did.
Marion... Marion!
Look, I'm sorry about that.
She just-- she took her
mother's death really hard.
Come on, let's get back to work.
Miss Layla?
Uh...
Kalos told me about
your Fairy Godmother idea.
I think it could be interesting.
Oh, I'm so glad you think so!
Provided, of course,
that all three people in
the routine are up to the task.
Yes, we're working hard!
Unfortunately I don't think
Sora and Anna are ready yet.
Charlotte and Julie are
more experienced performers,
so I'm suggesting them
for the roles.
But Sora and Anna are the
reasons why I suggested this--
This is not a slumber party.
They may be your friends, but
they're not the most competent
trampoline artists we have.
If you're not happy
with my casting changes
then you can step down, too.
Mia...
Come on, let's go.
But we--
It's okay. Layla's right.
Don't feel bad.
We're just better than you.
That's the way
things go sometimes.
You look like you
could use some coffee.
Huh? Oh, sorry, you scared me.
No, I'm sorry.
Marion said some
terrible things to you.
No it's okay, she's just a kid.
Still...
Besides, it kinda turned out
that she was
right about us anyway...
I'm sorry to hear that.
It seems like the three
of you were working so hard.
It's okay.
I'm sure Layla's right:
those girls are just
better than we are.
So, is Marion okay?
Oh, she will be once
she's finished sulking
in the rehearsal hall.
It's her favorite hiding place.
But she'll be back as soon
as she gets hungry enough.
Uh...?
What?
That stuff Marion
said about her mom.
Yeah?
It must be really rough
not having her around anymore.
I mean, she seemed really upset.
It's pretty rough on all of us
not having Cynthia around.
But Marion seems
to take it the hardest,
and sometimes things
really upset her.
My wife was
an amazing woman, Sora.
Six years ago she was
the star of Kaleido Stage.
She had talent like
you wouldn't believe.
Still, nobody worked
harder than she did.
You can never practice too much.
Talent will only get you so far.
If you really want to be
a star you have to work for it.
Every single day.
As Marion got older,
I think she started resenting
how much time
Cynthia spent working.
One day Marion got a fever.
She wanted Cynthia to stay
home with her, but Cynthia had
a show and there was no one
who could go on for her.
She had to perform.
And I guess maybe she
wasn't able to concentrate
like she normally did.
There was a terrible accident.
We got her
to the hospital alive,
but she was
slipping away from us.
Sweetheart, what are
you apologizing for?
I'm the one who made a mistake.
This is my fault, no one else's.
Once I get out of here I'll have
to practice harder than ever.
We can't have this
happen again, can we?
She died on the operating table.
Those were her last words.
Marion sort of shut down after
that. And she's gotten bitter,
because she doesn't think
anyone here is as good as
her mother was. Sorry to say
it, but you girls aren't the
first people she's yelled at.
I can understand why.
I mean, it sounds like she
loved watching her mother work.
She just wants everyone
at Kaleido Stage to be
as good as they can be.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I never
got to see her perform.
Sounds like I missed
something really great.
Listening to you talk about
how hard she worked makes
me realize that I well, I've
got a lot more practicing to do
before I'm ever gonna get on
stage here. I should go tell Mia
that I understand now.
Miss Layla was right. I wasn't
up to performance level.
Not yet. But that's why
I've gotta work hard, right?
'Morning, Marion.
Dad, she...
She's been practicing in here
for a couple of hours so far.
Says she's never gonna get
any better unless she works
really hard at it.
No!
Owww. Oh my gosh,
Anna! Are you okay?
I would be if you'd get offa
me. You should watch where
you're landing next time.
Sorry about that.
You think it's funny
you almost crushed me?
Let's get back to work.
Mia.
Where are Charlotte and Julie?
Shouldn't you guys
be practicing?
I gave up the role.
What?
But why'd you do that?
Well I decided I'd rather
perfect the Triple Illusion
with you.
And my Grandma always says
that good friends
should be cherished.
Mia...
Sorry, you guys.
It shouldn't have taken me
this long to do the right thing.
Are you sure this
is what you want to do?
Well, actually I haven't
given up the part just yet.
What?
He promised us three days.
We still have time
to get the Triple Illusion
working the way it should.
If it still doesn't work by the
deadline we'll resign our roles.
Okay.
Thank you.
I think those girls are gonna
be first-class Kaleido Stars.
Me, too.
Well then what
are we waiting for?
Right.
On the spins: I'll slow mine
down a little bit, but, Sora,
you need to speed yours up.
That sounds good.
And while you guys are busy
spinnin' around I'll throw in
a monkey pose.
No, you won't.
We've only got one day left,
so we've really gotta work.
I thought I saw Mommy...
Oh, it was nothing. Can we
get something to eat Daddy?
I thought you'd never ask.
The Star foretells hope.
What do you know?
She changed the future.
Everybody's here, so start
whenever you guys are ready.
Right.
What do you think?
These girls aren't
very polished performers.
But still, you were
on the edge of your seat
while they were
doing their routine.
They're pretty captivating;
I think all they need's
a push in the right direction.
Well, Kalos, it looks like you
have your work cut out for you.
I guess that means
they passed. For now anyway.
Sora, come home.
I won't get on that plane unless
you agree to come with me.
Just in time for the opening
of 'Cinderella' my Dad
decided to make
a surprise visit.
Sora's Dad wants her
to go back to Japan.
I know this is tough
for you but, Sora,
we've got a show to do.
I--I'm sorry, guys...
What?!
Now I have to decide
between the wishes of
my family and my dream.
What should I do? I wonder?
I wonder? I wonder?
Next time on Kaleido Star
'My Amazingly Distant Family'.
My wings are my dreams,
and on towards the sky...