Hey, everyone, Kaleido
Star's about to start,
so make sure your room is
brightly lit and that you're
not sitting too close to the TV.
My name is Sora Naegino.
Ever since I was a little
girl it's been my dream
to perform with Kaleido Stage.
So a few months ago I came
to the U.S. to give it a shot.
Boy, has it been an experience.
Everything is new to me,
and sometimes I'm a little lost.
But that's not going to keep me
from doing my best.
There's nothing I
can't do if I work hard!
Well, well, well.
Does everyone know the story
'The Little Mermaid?'
That's going to be
our next production,
and I'm trying out for the lead!
But I made a mistake
during the audition
and ended up getting hurt.
Now I'm terrified I'll make
the same mistake again, and it's
keeping me from performing.
I'm really in a pinch this time.
What'll I do, what'll I do?
It's lunchtime! I brought
you something to eat, Dad.
That was nice of you, Marion.
Everyone, it's time for a break.
I think we should
sit here today.
And now I'm going to
read you the story of
'The Little Mermaid.'
Once upon a time there was
a beautiful mermaid.
She lived at the bottom of the
ocean in an enormous palace...
'My Amazing Challenge
for the Lead Role.'
Great show, everyone!
Freedom! Yeah, I've been
wanting a vacation for so long
but now I don't know what to do.
I'm practicing.
We've gotta be
ready for the audition.
Didn't you hear about this? It's
on the last day of our vacation.
Nobody's told me
about an audition! Why?
It's posted on the bulletin
board at the dormitory.
So what's it for?
Last summer's production
of 'The Little Mermaid' was so
popular they're remounting it.
Whoa!
Uh, is something wrong?
I saw this show on video and it
was the most amazing thing ever!
I can't believe I'll
get to see it in person!
And now I might even get
a chance to be in it!
Oh, and it's the saddest
story, especially when
the Little Mermaid jumps off the
ship at the end-- every time
I see that I just cry and cry
and cry and cry and cry
and cry and cry...
All right, we get it.
And since Layla's wanting to try
out a few new trapeze maneuvers,
I heard they're looking for
a supporting cast
with trapeze experience.
Wow.
This could be your chance, Sora.
What?
'Cause the trapeze
is your thing.
What are you talking about?
After all, you mastered the
Golden Phoenix, didn't you?
Yeah...
Just think: you could
be a supporting player.
You really think so? Maybe
I should start practicing...
And the pay's higher
for supporting roles, too.
No way!
And they provide you
with a chauffeur.
Really? But what would
I need a chauffeur for?
Can you believe her?
She's acting like
she's already been cast.
Ugh, she makes me wanna hurl.
But there was a problem:
in order to trade her fins
for feet, the
Little Mermaid had to--
What in the world is going--
Oh, I'm sorry...
...uh, hi.
How are your
preparations coming along?
Everything is going
very smoothly.
I'm glad to hear it. Well, are
you gonna show me the production
or stand out here
and talk all day?
We haven't held auditions yet,
there's nothing to show.
Enough with your excuses, I want
to see where my money's going.
Show me what
you've got or deal's off.
Well I'm prepared to do
a scene for you if you'd like.
I mean, that way you'd
at least see something.
We're all aware that you're
a wonderful performer.
But doesn't Kaleido Stage
have anyone else?
Layla's good but I get
tired of seeing her show
after show after show.
Huh. That old man is just
as mean as the sea witch
in 'The Little Mermaid,'
isn't he Jonathan?
So have you got someone else?
In short, the audition
will be today and it will be
in front of our producer.
If one of you successfully
completes the audition
you'll play the title role.
However, if none of you
succeed we will be canceling
'The Little Mermaid's
run this summer.
That said, is anyone
ready to audition?
So if you screw up
the whole show's canceled?
Sounds too risky for me...
So none of you want to audition?
Sora, this is a great chance.
Why don't you do it?
You could be the
leading lady, you know.
Me as the Little Mermaid...?
What's that?
You say something, Boss?
That settles it then.
What?
Sora, you'll be auditioning
for the role today.
Me? But I thought the Little
Mermaid was Layla's part.
So what?
Weren't you just bragging
about your trapeze work?
I mean, it is
your specialty, right?
Huh.
And weren't you just
complaining about your salary?
Saying you should be
paid ten times more...
You know, so you could
buy that tropical island...
Well, Sora if you want
that much more money,
I highly recommend you take a
crack at this audition today.
But--
Is everything ready?
Ready.
Uh, Ken? What am I
supposed to do?
Don't worry, Sora.
I'm going to walk you through
everything you need to do, okay?
You're going to have to swing
from where you're standing
right now to the trapeze on
the other side of the set.
You'll do that when
I press the buzzer.
If you jump when I buzz, you'll
be in synch with the swing
on the other side
of the waterfall.
Waterfall? What are
you talking about?
We're ready when you are.
Yes, sir. We're starting.
Hey you'll do great,
just jump when I buzz, okay?
Jump when you hit
the buzzer, right.
So I can't see where I'm jumping
to because of the waterfall.
What am I gonna do?
Stop worrying and just do it!
Sora!
No, you're too late! Come back!
I-- I'm gonna make it!
Oh no.
But I-- I thought I had it.
Oh no...
I'm so glad. It's
good to see you awake.
You saved me, didn't you?
Yes. Well, you're talking,
so I think you'll be fine.
Uh, yes.
Thank you for everything.
Well I should be leaving now.
What? Oh no wait!
Where where are you going?
Our castle, Kaleido Stage.
Take me with you!
I'm sorry, but you
can't come this way.
Why not?
You'll never make it up there.
You should go back to
the world you belong to.
No. Please don't leave me here.
Don't go! Please come back!
Come back!
Don't leave me...
Hey! She's awake now.
Sora, are you okay?
I don't have fins. Thank god.
What was that?
Sora, you should
really take it easy.
They said that you slightly
dislocated your shoulder.
But if Yuri hadn't been there,
you'd be in a lot
worse shape right now.
What?
When Yuri saw you falling
he ran and he jumped on
stage to try and catch you.
And he had to give you
mouth-to-mouth and everything,
Sora.
So it wasn't just
a dream after all...
And then, when Ken saw Yuri
doing that, he got all --
Oh, I forgot about that.
Yeah, Ken got really
weird about it...
What?
Sora! Just what do you
think you're doing?!
What?
You know what!
You're supposed
to be taking it easy.
Didn't the doctor tell you
not to do this yet?
Oh, I'll be fine. I've gotta
show the producer I can do this
or else he'll cancel the show.
What what's wrong with me?
What-- oh my gosh,
what's going on?
I can't stop shaking.
What's wrong with me?
Sora. Sora.
Can you hear me? Sora?
What-- what happened?
You need to take it easy, okay?
Oh yeah, you know I think
you're right. I guess I'm not
quite healed yet. I think
I'll just go home and rest.
Wait a second.
What is it?
You need to tell me
the truth about this.
Are you afraid to swing again?
That's it, isn't it?
Sora if you're scared...
Hey Ken, why don't you
just butt out, okay?
You've gotta stop her.
Sora, you--
What up--
Sora...
What just happened here?
So how did it go?
I talked him into giving us
another chance next week.
Now we've just gotta hope
our performer's up for it.
Sora! Hey, Sora! The
dining hall's closing soon!
You're never gonna get better
if you don't eat something!
Please. Just leave me alone.
Oh, how pathetic.
You're so annoying.
Why did you skip practice today?
Because I'm injured, all right?
So injured you
can't get out of bed?
Look, my shoulder hurts...
How come?
Who cares? Just leave
me alone, all right?
You're going to end up like him.
Like who?
He was a man that was able
to see me a while ago.
And, just like you, he injured
himself on the trapeze.
He was never able to swing
again, too afraid of being hurt.
So did he have to
leave Kaleido Stage?
No.
How'd he do it? How did he
finally get rid of his fear?
So I was right:
none of this has anything to
do with your shoulder injury.
Hey, don't change the
subject, how'd he do it?
What's this?
The Hanged Man.
If you want to change
your current situation,
you need to face your fears.
What are you talking about?
The man that I was just telling
you about gradually became
unable to see me, Sora.
What is this...?
Sora.
Ken?
I knew you'd come back. I knew
you couldn't stay away for long.
I I'm sorry that
I snapped at you.
Hey, don't worry about it. I
never gave it a second thought.
I'm just so glad
you're back to practice.
After all, I set up
the trapeze for you.
So you set this up for me?
I worked all afternoon. So
that you'd feel comfortable.
I don't know what to say...
Well I should've guessed
you might be afraid
to get back up there.
How could you? I didn't
even know myself. But Ken,
don't you think these swings are
a little too low to practice on?
Well, the first thing we've
gotta do is get your confidence
back up, to erase the memory
of falling and being injured
from your mind.
How are we supposed to do that?
Practice. You'll just
keep doing it right 'til
you can't even remember
having done it wrong.
Still, don't you think having
them so low is just too easy?
You'll never know
unless you try.
I can't do this blind, Ken!
The blindfold's so you can
picture yourself doing it right.
But Ken--
I'll coordinate
the timing, okay?
Just jump after
I give the signal.
Are you ready, Sora?
I'm going to start.
Forget about the time
you made a mistake.
Just concentrate on
synchronizing with the sound.
Let's do this. One two three.
Sora, are you all right?
No, I'm sorry, Ken, but I I
just can't do this anymore.
Don't say that,
of course you can.
I'm sorry, I just can't do it.
Sora, listen to me.
You've got to trust me, okay?
There is no way
I'm going to let you fall.
I can't rescue you like Yuri
did, but I'm going to make sure
you play the Little Mermaid.
What do you say?
Okay. I'm ready to try it again.
One more time then?
Yes.
Who is this?
Sora, this is Master Lin,
my kung-fu teacher.
We thought he could teach you
his method of concentration,
so you can focus better when
you're up there on the trapeze.
What?
Stop whining, just try it.
Excellent! Master Lin
wants to give you a test.
Huh?
Oh, that means that if you can
keep up with him he'll teach you
his concentration method.
Right. Just don't be
too hard on me.
Oh wait...
Congratulations, Sora,
you passed the test.
What, I did?!
That's right.
Now take a deep breath
and try to clear your mind.
I'm all right.
Let's do it again.
I just can't get it.
Of course you can.
Master Lin says you've
shown amazing progress with
his concentration method.
Really?
You should really be
proud of yourself, Sora.
He's starting to move on to his
most advanced lessons for you.
What are you waiting for?
You can't expect him to
hold that position all day.
Sorry.
Clear all the clutter from your
mind and become one with nature.
Then you will be the wind,
the water and the earth.
You must become one with
all that surrounds you.
Only then will you know the
secret of true concentration.
Sora!
I must become one
with my surroundings...
Maybe we should take a break.
No, I wanna keep working.
I'm pretty sure
I've got it this time.
Well, Sora, it's almost
time for the audition.
But I was hoping to have
a little more recovery time.
The doctor tells me your
shoulder's completely healed.
Don't tell me you're
afraid of falling again.
If you're telling me you can't
perform, there's no reason
for you to be here anymore.
...there's no reason for you
to be here anymore...
Calm down, Sora. You have
nothing to worry about.
What are you talking about?
He just threatened to fire me
if I couldn't do it, okay?
But you know that
you can do this, Sora.
It was just practice! That's the
only reason I didn't freeze.
I'll never be able to do it
when it really counts!
I just can't swing anymore!
I can't... I can't...
I don't want to fall!
So you're giving it up
for the rest of your life?
A long time ago I decided
I couldn't swing again because
I was too afraid of being hurt.
I couldn't jump
even if I wanted to.
I felt the same way you
must be feeling right now.
But the truth
is you can do this.
When you were practicing the
Golden Phoenix I had no idea
how you could keep getting up
on that trapeze even though
it was such a tough practice.
But you mastered it. There are
a lot of great performers here
at Kaleido Stage, but, Sora,
you're the only one who ever
made me wish I hadn't quit.
Just try to remember
how good it feels when
you're performing, Sora.
Remember how good it feels
when you're performing...
Please don't give up.
You've got to try again.
I don't want my Sora
ruled by fear.
Sora...
Thank you, for everything.
Sora!
A blindfold?
Is she gonna make it?
Of course she will.
Start when you're ready.
Yes, sir. Let's do this,
Sora. Are you ready to go?
All right, then here we go.
One and two and three!
If you're telling me you can't
perform, there's no reason
for you to be here anymore.
Clear all the clutter from your
mind and become one with nature.
Then you will be the wind,
the water and the earth.
You must become one with
all that surrounds you.
Amazing!
You did it, Sora. You really
are the most incredible person
at Kaleido Stage.
You really are...
Congratulations! You're going
to be the Little Mermaid!
And so I got my
first leading role ever!
I tried to be just as good
as Layla was, but...
Our audiences
are getting smaller.
And our producer
isn't very happy.
I just don't get it. What am I
doing wrong? What, what, what?!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
'Facing an Amazing Wall.'
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...