Hey, everyone, Kaleido
Star's about to start,
so make sure your room is
brightly lit and that you're
not sitting too close to the TV.
My name is Sora Naegino.
Ever since I was a little
girl it's been my dream
to perform with Kaleido Stage.
So a few months ago I came
to the U.S. to give it a shot.
Boy, has it been an experience.
Everything is new to me,
and sometimes I'm a little lost.
But that's not going to keep me
from doing my best.
There's nothing I
can't do if I work hard!
Well, well, well, have you
ever met someone who seems
kind of unhappy all the time?
Rosetta seems like that to me...
But she's really amazing at
diabolo, and it looks like
I'm gonna have a chance
to perform with her.
The trouble is, I've never
done diabolo before.
Oh, what am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do?
Jonathan, come here! This way!
Wow, so this is his tank?
Kalos gave me instructions
about where it could be and
what it would look like.
And it looks like
Jonathan's really enjoying
what we came up with.
It's amazing!
It's so big.
Looks like he's
enjoying himself out there.
Jonathan! Come here!
Jonathan!
He snubbed us.
The ingrate.
I guess things'll be
different now that he's
not living in my bathtub.
Marion, Vince has come back
from the market already.
Did ya hear that?
It's lunchtime!
Vince! Hurry up,
he's really hungry!
That girl...
'The Amazing Girl
Who Doesn't Smile.'
Okay, Rosetta, your provisional
contract is for one week.
After I see you perform,
I'll make the decision
whether to keep you
on here or not.
I hope you understand: this is
our standard business practice.
Who is she?
Don't you know? She's that
diabolo prodigy from France.
She's great, a total genius!
She's sort of a hero of mine...
Sora?
What're you doing?
Uh, we were just
passing by and we tripped.
We weren't eavesdropping
or anything--
Just stop.
Sora, Kalos wants you.
But what for?
He wants you to take care
of a special guest
we'll have staying
with us this week.
Really?!
This is Sora Naegino.
She'll take you to your room
so you can get some rest
after your long trip.
That's right, I'm Sora.
Nice to meet you.
Well, I'll see you later, then.
I look forward to it.
This is so exciting! I'm
a huge fan of yours. I--
Nice to meet you.
I'm Mia.
And I'm Anna.
Nice to meet you.
Is Layla Hamilton here?
Oh, she won't be here
until closer to show time.
Oh. Right.
Your luggage has already
been taken to your room.
I'll take you to your room,
okay? Right this way, Rosetta.
Um, Boss? Thank you for building
that pool for Jonathan.
He seems to really like it!
So this is where you'll
be staying, Rosetta!
The sea breeze is really nice,
so I'll just leave
a window open...
Sora?
Yes?
Am I to understand
that Kalos has put me
in the same kind of room
he gives to his students?
Huh?
I'm the youngest diabolo
world-champion ever,
and I've won that title for
the past four years running.
I know! I watched
your competitions on TV.
You were really incredible!
And I remember when
they interviewed you--
you were so poised even
though you were so young.
That's why I remembered
what you said.
You're French-born, you've been
doing diabolo since you could
walk and you travel from circus
to circus all by yourself!
I'm Belgian.
What?
I was born in Belgium and
I started studying in France.
How are you supposed to be
my caretaker when you
know nothing about me?
Oh. You must be tired.
So how was it, Sora?
Kaleido Stage is proud
to present Rosetta,
the youngest person
ever to hold the title
of diabolo world-champion.
And if you feel like practicing
for the championship yourself,
stop by our gift shop and
pick up your own diabolo set...
Uh, Rosetta?
We were just wondering...
...if you would
maybe teach us diabolo?
According to my contract,
I don't perform unless
I'm on stage in front of an
audience. Please shut the door
behind you, otherwise
I can't concentrate.
Right. Sorry.
What a spoiled brat.
I just wanted
to learn diabolo...
She's amazing.
She's a genius.
She is amazing. But why-- why
isn't she more fun to watch?
Watching her is like
watching a diabolo machine.
Mama! I'm bored!
I know, but there'll be
a clown on stage after this.
And now it's time
for intermission, folks!
Rosetta, welcome
to Kaleido Stage.
Oh Layla, how was
my performance on stage?
It was absolutely perfect.
Not a single mistake.
That means a lot to me, Layla.
I'm going to enjoy
watching you this week.
I'm gonna be around
a lot longer than that.
You sound really sure of that.
I am.
Rosetta. I'd like to talk
to you, do you have a minute?
Oh, you wanna extend
my contract, right?
Actually, I was going to
terminate your contract.
You want me to do a
routine that's more geared
toward little kids?
I'm going to pay you
for the rest of this week,
but I don't want to
see you on stage again.
Let's go everyone,
the show's about to start.
I will want to hear
your explanation for this
in my dressing room.
I'll be right back.
Sora! We're about to go on!
Rosetta, it goes without
saying that you're
very skilled at diabolo.
That's why I invited you.
But I watched the audience
while you were on stage
performing today.
And I didn't see a single person
who was enjoying your show.
Then I'll just
rearrange my routine
to make it more interesting.
Rosetta, I'm sorry, but--
I didn't make a single mistake!
It was a perfect performance.
It's not my fault if your
audience is too stupid
to appreciate what I do.
I see, so you're blaming
this on the audience?
You're right and
they're wrong, is that it?
I've been the world champion
for four consecutive years.
I'm better at this
than anyone else.
Kaleido Stage can only
stay alive as long as
the audience keeps coming back.
And I got the feeling that
they wouldn't come
back to see you.
That's stupid!
Why wouldn't they?
Because this is not
an athletics competition
where you show off your skills.
Excuse me...
I'll explain all of this
to your booking agent.
Ken, when you have time
you should take Rosetta
over to Marine Park...
But, Boss...
Don't treat me
like I'm a child!
Rosetta!
Watch out!
What's going on?
What's her problem?
She sure can run fast.
But, Boss, are you sure
you don't want to give her
another chance before
you send her away.
I'm sure.
She's not a performer.
But she only did one show...
One show is enough sometimes.
She needs a second chance.
She can do better
if you just let her try.
I'll give Rosetta another
shot on one condition.
Yes? What is it?
You do the show with her.
What's that?
I'm giving you six days
to turn her around.
In that time you need
to use your talent to make her
act worth watching.
But-- I didn't mean--
Six days.
But-- Boss, wait!
Uh I've never done diabolo
before in my life.
This could be good for you.
A turning point in your career.
But I've been performing
without any mistakes!
It was enough to be perfect
when you were little.
Now that you're older,
people expect more of you.
The job offers aren't coming in
like they used to, you know.
You need to stay there.
See what you can learn.
But I didn't do
anything wrong...
Are you all right, Sora?
Not at all.
Why don't you just
tell him you can't?
Yeah. I'm sure
he'll understand.
But I've got to try!
Of course you do.
Oh no, Miss Sarah, we've
got a problem! Come quick!
What's going on?
Rosetta's gone missing!
That is a problem.
Do you think she
could've left for home?
What, at this hour?
Rosetta! Rosetta!
Rosetta! Oh no, where could
she be?! Rosetta! Rosetta!
Sora! I found her!
What?
Oh. I'm so glad!
What was Kalos thinking,
pairing me with you?
You think that you can do this?
Well, I'll never find out
unless I try, will I?
You know, it's weird, but
when I get all worried about
making mistakes I end up
having a worse performance
than if I just let
myself have some fun.
I don't go on stage to make
mistakes. What's the point
of doing it if you
can't do it flawlessly?
There's no way I'll ever be
as good as you are,
so the least I can do
is be entertaining.
I mean, I can't be perfect, so
I'll just have to do my best.
Working hard?
Ken!
I brought you these just
in case you needed extras.
Wow. Where did you
get all those?
I stocked up on
them a while ago.
I was wondering what
I'd do with all these.
So this is my fault?
Sorry. I didn't
mean it like that.
The audience didn't
enjoy my show, so I'm out.
I get it, all right?
But, Rosetta, I didn't mean...
I don't know if we can do this.
If you can't
it's not your fault.
What?
You know she was just nine
years old when she won
her first world-championship?
And she was just five when
she started studying diabolo.
I don't know about you,
but when I was five,
I was crazy about Kaleido Stage.
I couldn't get enough of it.
I was, too.
I don't think Rosetta's ever
had the chance to appreciate it
as a member of the audience.
Ken! I think I've got an idea...
The airport, please.
She's leaving!
Okay.
Ken?
'You don't have to be perfect if
you do your best?' Why bother?
Hmm. Uh, Miss? Do you know
those people on the bike?
They've been following us
for quite a while.
What do you want?
Sora wanted you to see
her show before you leave.
Do I have to?
Sure do.
Go, Jonathan!
Catch!
What's going on here?!
You've got his fish!
Good job, Jonathan!
I'll trade you! Oh, no.
I can't reach it, Jonathan!
That was great!
Yay Jonathan!
Rosetta! You're just in time.
I can't stay for long.
Come watch Rosetta!
Just jump in!
Got it!
Aw, give Sora a break!
Jonathan's better than she is.
Jonathan!
You give that back!
Jonathan! Come back here!
Give that back! Come back!
Give it! Hey, look!
Ta da, yay!
You're incredible, Sora!
Weird, isn't it?
What is?
When I watch her perform
I get really nervous
she'll make a mistake. I'm
always on the edge of my seat.
It's always so exciting to
watch her because she does make
a lot of mistakes, but every
once in a while she pulls off
a trick and it's
unbelievable, like magic.
You should go watch her
tonight, see what you think.
Watch Sora perform?
Here!
It's amazing. Nothing like
the performances I give.
Sora...
Sora?
Rosetta! You came
to see the show!
I want to perform diabolo with
you if you're still interested.
I'd like that.
You can do your act perfectly
and I'll just have to
try my best. So whaddya
think about that, huh?
That's gonna be one
interesting routine.
But it's never gonna work
unless Sora gets a little bit
more comfortable doing diabolo.
Let's just get started.
Wrong!
Okay!
Do it like you're
going at the diabolo.
Don't actually collide with it.
Right...
The Devil in its
upright position.
It means she'll have to
make extraordinary efforts.
That was awful. Again.
And she's not even here
to appreciate the
readings I do for her...
This-- this-- this
is totally impossible!
We only have one day left
until our performance.
This is no time to lie around.
It looks like
they've made the deadline.
Building the set on such
short notice wasn't easy.
Sorry about that.
Well it is an
interesting idea.
Did they come up
with this on their own?
Yeah.
They're a good team.
And now it's time for
Kaleido Stage's first ever
diabolo battle!
In this corner, we have the
world-champion, Rosetta!
And in this corner, with only
five days' diabolo experience,
is Sora.
Ready? Battle!
Got it.
Yes.
Lookin' good! Let's go, Sora!
You can do it, Rosetta!
Here!
Yeah?
I lost it!
Rosetta made a mistake!
I know!
And Rosetta wins it!
They did it!
Sora's amazing!
Rematch!
Bravo! Bravo!
Rosetta became
a performer after all...
Sora? When I was
nine years old I won
the diabolo world championship
for the first time.
In the interviews
there was always a crowd
standing behind the press.
They were the ones who
watched the competition,
and they seemed
so glad to be there.
I remember feeling
so proud to perform diabolo.
I'd completely forgotten
how happy it made me.
I'd forgotten how much
I used to love diabolo.
But I remember it now.
Thanks to Kaleido Stage and
thanks to you, too, Sora.
Oh. Oh, Rosetta, I--
That's so sweet!
It's awesome!
I owe this all to you.
Thanks for everything, Sora.
Wow...
So, you're leaving anyway?
Yeah. I'll miss you, Sora.
The show yesterday was a
great success thanks to you.
It was a thrill
to watch your act.
Well, I really learned a lot in
my week here at Kaleido Stage.
I wish you'd consider staying
on with us a little longer.
I can't.
Are you getting back
at me for last week?
No, I just wanna go home
and get in touch with
why I love diabolo again.
Cheer up.
You look like your girlfriend
just broke up with you, Boss.
Yeah, that's kinda
how it feels...
Buh bye!
Good luck, Rosetta!
Merci, Sora.
You should tap into
your commercial value.
And so Layla's father
came to Kaleido Stage,
but he left without seeing
the show. It seems like he
thinks of her as just some
kind of a business tool.
He even tried to make up
for missing her birthday
by throwing his money around.
Well, if he's going to be
that way, we'll have to make
her birthday party
a success on our own, right?
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
'An Amazing Star,
Even In Tough Times.'
My wings are my dream,
and on toward the sky...