Hey, everyone, Kaleido
Star's about to start,
so make sure your room is
brightly lit and that you're
not sitting too close to the TV.
My name is Sora Naegino.
Ever since I was a little
girl it's been my dream
to perform with Kaleido Stage.
So a few months ago I came
to the U.S. to give it a shot.
Boy, has it been an experience.
Everything is new to me,
and sometimes I'm a little lost.
But that's not going to keep me
from doing my best.
There's nothing I
can't do if I work hard!
Well, well, well.
What's your father like?
Is he really kind
or kind of harsh?
Layla's father works
so hard that he has no idea
what's going on with her.
Sometimes he makes me
really feel sorry for Layla.
But, no matter what, I'm
gonna make sure her birthday
is fantastic!
I will, I will, I will!
So how 'bout it, guys,
can I throw in a monkey pose
at the end of the show today?
No way.
Man...
Oh, sorry.
This is your chance!
Quick, before the moment
passes say something funny!
That's all right 'cause... uhh.
It's no use! I'm
awful at ad-libbing.
I thought it was funny.
That's one enormous bouquet.
Yeah. I'm taking it to Layla.
Her father, Mr. Hamilton,
had it sent over.
Oh does he come here often?
Nah, he's usually too busy
with work to come visit.
Yeah, he's the founder of
the Hamilton Hotel chain.
Hamilton Hotels? I think we
have one of those in Japan.
Yeah, they're
all over the place.
Wow...
Well I'd better
get these to Layla.
He must be nice.
'An Amazing Star,
Even In Tough Times.'
I think Cinderella is going to
be one of her signature roles.
How's the box office on it?
It's the best seller
Kaleido Stage has ever had.
Good. Who are these
Fairy Godmothers?
They passed the
audition this year.
Hello, Father.
There you are, Layla.
Congratulations on your play.
Oh thank you. And thanks
for the beautiful flowers.
They're nowhere near as
beautiful as you are, Layla.
Do you think that this time
you'll have a chance to see
my show while you're in town?
I don't have the time.
I'm having a party tonight
for some big business people.
Make sure you come by
after your performance.
I will.
Kalos, I'd like
you to escort her.
It would be my pleasure.
And invite those Fairy Godmother
girls for me, would you?
Why are you inviting them?
It'll be good exposure
for them. Besides, you won't
be a Kaleido Star forever.
I'm keeping my eye on
the future of this place.
See you tonight.
He's a very busy man.
Yeah. He's so busy that
he's never seen one of my
performances
all the way through.
We did it perfectly again!
It's like they couldn't wait
for the transformation scene
to come! This is the
greatest audience, you guys.
The act would be even better if
I added a pratfall at the end.
It would not.
I'm with Mia.
I had to try...
Just because you've had a few
good performances don't think
you can start messing around.
We won't.
But we did a perfect show today.
Looks like she's
just in a rotten mood.
Maybe she's just a little
more tense because her dad's
in the audience this time.
But he left before
the show even started.
Oh. I didn't know that...
You three.
Go to the costume room.
A party?!
This is so awkward.
Say something to
break the ice, Sora.
It's a shame your father
couldn't stay to see
the show today.
Well it's really nothing new.
I-- I'm so sorry.
How awkward.
Is that Layla Hamilton?
You look stunning, Layla.
Thank you, Father.
What is it, Sora?
You okay?
I feel completely
out of place here.
And now I'm fine.
I'm more nervous here than
I've ever been on stage.
Me, too.
They're sure getting
a lot of attention.
Yes.
Before I forget, have you
met that man over there?
Uh, I've seen him before.
If I'm remembering right,
he's a movie producer.
That's right. And I hear
he's looking for a heroine
for his next feature film.
I want you to audition for him.
So Layla wants to be
a movie star as well?
This would be
a great career move.
From the top box-office
star at Kaleido Stage
to the top box-office
star in the world.
Your commercial value
could triple, easily.
I'll do it.
But, Layla... Layla!
Didn't I see you three
in the newspapers?
Aren't you girls the Fairy
Godmothers? You're just darling!
How do you do that
pumpkin thing-ma-bob?
Could you do it here for us?
Oh, yes! Please
perform something!
What do we do?
Let's put on a show.
I was just gonna suggest that.
What?
Come on Sora, just go with it!
Let's do this.
Catch!
This party's turning out
to be fun fun fun!
Ta-dah!
What are they doing?
Here, Sora!
Heads up!
Yeah!
Huh. They're not bad.
You should come to
see 'Cinderella'--
they have this triple--
Thanks a lot! Thanks!
Come to see us
at Kaleido Stage, okay?
And now it's time
for some party jokes!
Ladies...
Oh, hello, Mr. Hamilton.
I want to ask you a favor.
Tomorrow happens to be
my daughter's birthday.
We'll be having a party
at our house in the afternoon.
And I hope the three of you
will be able to attend.
We'd love to! Oh,
and then you could take
the rest of the day off work
after the party and see Layla
on stage in 'Cinderella.'
I have business
to attend to tomorrow.
But--
You'll be fairly compensated
for your time at the party,
so don't be late.
Hey, hold on a minute.
I'm a busy man.
I just wanted to tell you we'd
love to go to Layla's party.
You don't have to pay us for--
That's awfully selfless of you.
But you'll never be
a success that way.
He's awful!
Well it's really nothing new.
Poor Layla.
She must be so lonely.
I don't want Mr. Hamilton's
money, but I figure we've got to
go to the party just so we can
try to cheer Layla up, you know?
Um--
So that's what we'll do.
But--
What is it?
Oh nothing. You won't
listen to me anyway...
What?
It's canceled?
Yes. There is no party.
What's going on here?
Then can you make sure Layla
gets her birthday present?
What are you doing here?
Didn't you hear me,
what are you doing here?
We came to wish you a...
...happy birthday!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
My father invited you,
didn't he?
Yes.
How come you canceled
all of a sudden?
It wasn't sudden.
Every year my father
gets people to come to
my party by paying them.
And that... really
means nothing to me.
It would take
the fun out of it.
That's why I always
cancel it. Every year.
Then why doesn't your father
stop throwing these parties
for you if you can't
enjoy them anyway?
That's just the way things are.
He may not know
how to make me happy,
but he cares about me
in his own way.
That should be enough,
shouldn't it?
But that's--
Well, it's enough for me.
Now please go back home.
Okay.
I really have to practice now.
You practice here?
At your house?
Of course.
Wow.
This is huge...
How cool is that, to have a
practice room in your house?
So do you spend a lot of
your time in here, Layla?
Practicing, I mean.
Unless I'm rehearsing
for a new production,
I'm in here
a few hours every day.
More when I've had
a bad performance.
That's a lot. And you don't
take your birthday off?
One of these days my father is
going to acknowledge my work
at Kaleido Stage.
And when he does I want to be
the best performer
I can possibly be.
But doesn't he doesn't
he want to you be
a movie star instead now?
So I'll audition for the movie.
I'm going to live up
to his expectations.
I want him to be proud of me.
So you've seen my practice room.
Now I have to get to work.
Right. We'll just
get out of your way.
Then it's settled.
What? What's settled?
And then once the show's
over, our curtain call can be
one giant party
for Layla's birthday!
Wouldn't that be great?!
But if we're gonna do this we
have to get to work right away.
Mia, you'll be the director.
Ken and Jean will be in
charge of sets. Anna and Sarah
can throw some costumes
together for us.
And I'll find a job
for you, Marion.
Now there's not much time
'til the next show. Get going.
Hm? Well, what are all
of you standing around for?
Come on, get to work!
Once she gets an idea
in her head she sure goes
all the way with it.
It's one of the
nicest things about her.
I couldn't agree more.
So is there some kind of
trick to sewing this stuff?
Just do your best,
I'll fix it later.
What...
I like painting!
Good job there, Marion.
You all set?
Ready.
I can't wait to see
the look on Layla's face.
Ha yeah, me neither.
Are you girls planning
something again?
Yeah. We're throwing birthday
party for Layla after the show.
But, please, keep it
a secret, all right?
I wouldn't spoil the surprise.
Good. Thanks a lot, Yuri!
Listen up. Jonathan, you've
got a very important role:
you're handing Layla
the cake, you understand?
All right...
I think we're just
about ready to go.
No, not quite yet.
Just one more thing
and we'll be done.
What? You're kidding, right?
Of course not.
But, Sora, it's
just not possible.
Can't you at least ask?
I'll ask him, but he...
You think it won't work.
Well. I guess it was
too much to hope for...
Hey, don't worry.
I'll ask him anyway.
Really?
Yes. But I'm not
promising anything.
Thank you Ken!
You're welcome.
Yes. She needs to
speak to Mr. Hamilton.
It's regarding his daughter,
Layla Hamilton,
and her performance
tonight at Kaleido Stage.
Her name is Sora Naegino.
Uh, well she's one
of our new people--
I'm not suspicious.
I am a Fairy Godmother!
Uh that didn't
sound suspicious...
Excuse me, Mr. Hamilton.
You have a phone call.
Take a message.
She says it's urgent.
She says she's a,
uh, Fairy Godmother?
Would you like me to
contact the police, sir?
No. I'll take it.
I'm sorry I interrupted
your meeting.
My secretary said it was urgent.
Did you change your mind about
being paid for the party?
The party was canceled.
What?
She cancels it every year.
Layla uses the time
to practice instead.
That's ridiculous.
So we're throwing her
a party tonight after the show.
And I I know it would mean the
world to her if you would come.
That's impossible.
Impossible or not,
you should still be here.
The best thing would be if you
came for the show and then--
It would take me four hours to
get to Cape Mary by private jet.
So there's no way I could
make it to the show on time.
It doesn't matter if you're
a little late, just come!
I appreciate your concern.
Thank you for telling me
about Layla's cancellation.
I'm glad I finally know
how she feels after
all these years.
No you don't know, sir.
You don't have a clue,
do you? Don't you understand?
No matter how many people
are around her, if the person
she wants to be there isn't
she feels lonelier than ever.
I think she's really lonely,
Mr. Hamilton, and I think
that's why she
canceled your party.
Layla needs to know that you
care about her, so please,
please say you'll
be here tonight.
Don't miss her
birthday this year.
But her father's
never going to come.
But Sora decided
to call him, anyway.
He'll never do it.
I don't know. Sora can
be very persuasive...
Yes?
Layla, do you have a second?
What is it?
Well we heard that your
father's going to be out there
in the audience tonight.
He's not. Now go.
But today's your birthday.
There's no way he'd miss that...
Hey what is this?
Happy birthday, Layla!
Happy birthday, Layla.
From all of us.
Sora.
This is from the company.
We hope you like it.
And now for the present...
Is it...
Yeah!
Yeah! Happy Birthday Layla!
Yeah! That was so awesome!
We pulled it off.
But the most important thing is
that Layla enjoyed it, too--
Are you insane? You're the one
who planned this, aren't you?
Yes, I did.
I wish you hadn't.
I've never felt so publicly
humiliated before in my life.
I I'm so sorry.
Don't you ever do
something like this again.
But wait! Layla?
What? There's not more,
is there?
At least take the cake,
I mean well I don't care about
the cake but there's
a message on top.
It's a note from your father,
he told me to give it to you
when I was on the
phone with him today.
Mind your own business.
I thought it turned out
really well.
You tried to do
a nice thing, Sora.
You did the best you could.
It just wasn't good enough.
I knew Layla'd hate having
a party like this...
It's a note from your father,
he told me to give it to you
when I was on the
phone with him today.
Don't you ever do
something like this again.
What's wrong with me?
What am I so irritated about?
Happy birthday, Layla.
From all of us.
I should've known she
wouldn't want a party.
But we all
thought she'd like it.
I guess some people just
don't like parties...
You know, the worst part about
all of this is I ended up
ignoring her feelings
just like her father did
in the first place.
What do you wanna do with
the cake? Should we eat it?
It doesn't look like
Layla's going to want it.
I'm going to make sure
she gets that message
from her father anyway.
But Sora...
That might make her mad
all over again.
Well I'm used to
people being mad at me.
Sora! I'm coming in!
Okay.
It's still here. That's great. I
thought you would've eaten it...
Do you want some?
No. Layla's maid is downstairs.
She came to pick up the cake.
She said she'll accept the cake
since you took the
trouble to bake it.
Really! Layla can be
so strange sometimes.
If that's all, I'll leave
the cake here. Good night.
A fax?
Happy birthday, Layla, forever
sparkling star of my heart.
You're my little Kaleido star.
I guess it's always hard...
I just realized kids
sometimes can't talk to their
real parents either. I wonder
if every family's like that.
They are as far as I can tell.
That's too bad.
You could talk to me.
You know, if you wanted to
get something off your chest.
No thanks.
Happy birthday, Layla.
Don't you have any stars
other than this Layla person?
They're holding auditions for
the lead in our next show,
'The Little Mermaid.' I just
have to try for that part.
Sora made a mistake, then she
was so scared of getting hurt
she couldn't jump anymore.
Don't worry, Sora.
Trust me, all right?
What's gonna happen to me if
I can't perform? What? What?
Next time on Kaleido Star,
'My Amazing Challenge
for the Lead Role.'
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...