Hello everybody!
Kaleido Star's about to start.
While you're watching
make sure the room is well lit,
and don't sit too
close to the TV!
Well, well, well.
Have any of you
ever told someone
how you really felt about them?
Maybe told them
that you love them?
Just the idea of it
makes me nervous.
Mr. Policeman has decided
to ask Miss Kate to marry him!
That Mr. Policeman.
He may be a big guy, but
he's definitely got a soft side.
He's even a little shy.
Be brave Mr. Policeman!
Remember, it's all about
courage, right Ken?
Hey, what's wrong with you,
you look kinda pale...
What if I made you
become my partner.
Hey, let me go,
stop, you're hurting me!
Are you the one?
Are you the one that
can become my partner?
Sophie!
Leon?
Sophie.
I'm so happy.
I saw a side of Leon that
I've never seen before.
It was different than his
regular cold personality.
He was kind.
And so sad.
But Leon likes to compete.
And I've decided I'm not
gonna do that anymore.
So I can't become his partner.
The dream that
I have is different
from Leon's and Layla's.
It's my dream and mine alone.
Someday when
I get back on stage,
I'll finally create
my dream show.
One with no competitions,
that everyone can enjoy.
That's the kind of Kaleido Stage
that I wanna be a part of.
"Mr. Policeman's
Amazing Proposal."
There she is!
Wow, I'm really nervous.
I knew that you were gonna
be too nervous to do this.
That's why I came prepared.
Okay Jonathan, give it to him!
You brought me a book?
The Perfect Dating Manual: 100
Ways To Captivate Her Heart!
Listen, if you don't want to
lose Sora to Leon I suggest
you start reading that book and
captivate her heart, got it?
I'm dressed like
a coffee machine...
Oh don't worry about it,
that getup really suits you!
Thanks, but you're not helping.
Besides, if she sees me dressed
up like a vending machine,
she'll think I've
teamed up with Anna.
And what's wrong with that?
A woman in trouble
is your best target.
While you tenderly console her,
take advantage of her
confusion and ask her
out on a date, oh yeah!
Make sure you take her
out for a nice pricey lunch,
and then her heart
will be yours.
You've got my guarantee.
Alright guys, now's your chance
to shoot for the stars, oh yeah.
No way, that book
won't help at all.
What?
You'd better at least go out
there and cheer her up a bit.
But...
Thanks for always
helping me Ken.
He's not my
boyfriend or anything.
So what did you
wanna talk about?
Hey Ken, I didn't see you there!
Guts are what make a man!
Guts are what make a woman!
Life is all about guts,
so get out there Ken!
It's Sora!
Hey, are you okay?
Did I hurt you?
Talk to me please!
A woman in trouble is
your best target, yeah!
This isn't the time for that.
Are you alright Sora?
Ken!
Sorry, I wasn't looking where
I was going and I ran into you.
That's okay.
So are you gonna visit
someone at the hospital too?
Like Leon?
And why are you dressed
like a coffee machine?
Yeah, I know that
I must look pretty silly,
but I've been waiting
to ask if maybe
you'd like to go
to lunch with me.
You're asking me out?
Is he doing this to
try to cheer me up?
He must be...why else would
he be dressed like that?
I haven't done anything
but worry people lately.
That's it!
I'll go to lunch and have so
much fun that he'll
be surprised!
I would love to Ken!
You know, I was just
starting to get hungry.
Oh really!
Let's go!
Okay!
That outfit looks
pretty good on you.
You think?
Yeah!
So does this mean
you're teaming up with Anna?
I'm gonna go change now.
They've walked away!
So how'd it go?
I can't tell.
Then let's follow them.
It's a great restaurant,
and it's got a spectacular
view from the terrace.
In fact I was just
there last week
with a friend from
middle school.
Really?
We just have
to turn this corner.
And there's a...Laundromat
that's...shut...down...oh man.
Well maybe if we turn
that corner over there!
And there's a bowling alley
that's been shut down.
Let's turn that corner there!
And now we're at the ocean.
How in the world
could that happen.
Hey, do you think that maybe
the map in that book is wrong?
There's no way that
map can be wrong.
My dad used it when he
went on dates with my mom.
How many years ago was that?
How should I know?
That was a really long time
ago before I was even born.
Look, what's Ken
doing over there?
He's relying on
that stupid book!
So what should I do now?
In unexpected
situations you have
to make the
appropriate decisions.
Let's say the restaurant you
wanna go to is closed down.
If you're a smart guy,
then you've explored
the area for other
places to eat nearby.
Don't worry, I'll be your
guide to the power of love.
Sora?
Sora!
Maybe we expected
too much from him...
Ken!
There's a hot
dog stand over here.
I guess hot dogs will do.
I don't see a terrace, but we've
got a great view of the ocean.
Sounds good!
This is yummy!
Hanging outside when the
weather's nice is the best!
Thank you so much for
inviting me to lunch Ken.
No problem, you're welcome!
Wait a minute, why is she
the one cheering me up?
That's it!
I'm the man,
I have to take the lead!
So, really great
weather today, huh?
Yeah, it's really nice!
Now what do I talk about?
I...just need
a little...courage...
Hey look, it's Mr. Policeman!
Mr. Policeman!
Oh, it's you Sora.
Sora!!
Mr. Policeman please slow down,
you're gonna knock me over!
I'm begging you please,
you gotta help me!
Of course, Mr. Policeman.
You wanna propose to Miss Kate?
That's the plan.
You see, I've had this dream to
make a romantic proposal by
my thirtieth birthday ever
since I was a kid.
But I don't know...
You're worried she's
gonna dodge the question,
so you're afraid to even
ask it in the first place.
You understand me!
Completely, in fact I feel your
pain as if it were my own!
Um I hate to
interrupt your moment,
but when is your thirtieth
birthday Mr. Policeman?
Well Sora...today's my birthday.
Today?
Are you serious?
I am.
Then you've gotta hurry up and
go see Miss Kate right now!
That's the problem...she's
on vacation from work
and she's not at home.
I took the day
off and everything,
but my dream still
isn't gonna happen.
I guess it means that dreams are
better off just staying dreams.
Mr. Policeman...
"Dreams are better off
just staying dreams"?
No way!
Our dreams are goals that
we can make happen!
We do whatever we can
to make them reality.
Mr. Policeman?
Yeah?
Come on Mr. Policeman.
Let's make your dream come true!
Sora.
Well, let's go!
Yeah!
This is a strange
turn of events...
That's okay, all that matters
is Sora's smiling!
First things first,
we've gotta find Miss Kate.
Do you think we'll
be able to find her?
Sometimes if
you've got bad timing
it makes everything
else more difficult.
Maybe it's hopeless after all.
Come on, don't be so
pessimistic, your chance will
definitely come,
you've just gotta believe!
Right, I just gotta believe!
Just like she said, I can't
lose heart and give up.
I gotta believe that
my chance will come!
Look!
Isn't that Miss Kate?
Hi, how're you doing Kate?
Were you waiting long Robert?
It looks like I've got
no chance of winning.
That's not true!
Women don't just care about
looks or brains or money,
they like a man that's
warm and sincere too.
Miss Kate knows what
a great guy you are,
she thinks you're a great catch!
Okay, I'm gonna go
find out what's going on.
Hey Sora, what do
you mean by 'find out'?
There she goes.
You know...if this dream
isn't gonna happen,
I think I'd rather wake up.
I'm bored.
You're bored!?
How do you think I feel?!
I'm tired of doing this stupid
exercise over and over again!
Yeah, now that's
what I wanna see!
I wanna see that
kind of intensity
and feeling in your acting.
You had a great presence
when you were on stage with
Leon and Sora, do you remember
the audience's reaction?
Um, no.
Oh man, this is gonna
take longer than I thought.
What kind of
special training is this?
Is this some kind of
performance art?
Maybe they're shooting for TV.
They look a bunch of weirdos.
It might be best
to avoid eye contact.
This keeps getting more
and more complicated.
We've gotta be sneaky and
make sure they don't spot us.
If anyone finds out, I won't
be able to go to school.
Oh, Robert's just
a co-worker of mine.
He went shopping
with me today to
help me find
something for a friend.
Okay, that makes sense.
But why're you asking?
Well, there's something
I wanted to ask you...
I guess that hot
dog wasn't enough.
Say, why don't we go
get something to eat?
It's pay day today,
so it'll be my treat.
I just have to run
by the bank real quick.
I gotta tell them
everything's cool!
I have no clue
what she's trying to say...
You're not making me
feel any better.
Come on!
Why are they locking up?
I've got a bad
feeling about this...
Sora!
What is it?
What's going on?
You don't think it's a
bank robbery, do you?
No way...
Hand over all your money!
Don't try anything!
I'm the unluckiest guy in the
world I got nothing to lose!
No, Kate!
Jerry?
Mr. Policeman, Ken!
Policeman?
You're kidding!
Nope, that's right.
So you'd better
let go of Kate now.
No...no...no...no,
that's just my luck!
My first bank robbery ever and
I've got a policeman
as a hostage?
This sucks!
I really am the unluckiest
guy in the world.
Listen up you guys,
I'm serious about this!
I'm not leaving til I get all
your cash, so all of you on
the second floor
better get down here quick.
Hey you, tie up the
policeman with this.
Who, me?
Yeah you, hurry up.
Yes sir.
And make sure you
tie him up tightly,
cuz I'm gonna check
your work later!
If you need some more rope, then
I got plenty in my bag, okay?
Preparation is the
one thing I'm good at,
that's what grandma
always used to say.
Sorry about this.
Don't worry.
Just do what he says
or we'll be in danger.
Go ahead and tie it tightly.
Listen!
It's a patrol car!
What!?
You've gotta be kidding!
I told you not to try anything
and you go and call the police?
Oh man, could
things get any worse?
Nobody called the police,
they already knew
cuz this bank is monitored
by police security cameras
The bank is?
Nobody told me that.
But even if someone told
me it wouldn't matter
cuz I'm the unluckiest
guy in the world!
It looks like it really
is a bank robbery.
Sora!
Attention felon!
Release the hostages immediately
and come out with your hands up!
We can see everything happening
inside the bank on our monitors.
Yeah!
It looks like all
the hostages are safe.
If you come out now
you won't have any
major criminal
charges against you.
You may not like the
way your life has gone,
but you know what?
--Neither do we!
--Can you see it?
--Yeah.
--Uh, kinda.
There they are!
I can't stand in front of people
and say it, but it's not a lot!
Sora and Ken are alright!
I hate the world.
It's full of phonies
that have nothing better
to do than to give
me a hard time.
But today was
supposed to change that.
I guess not now.
All I wanted was
to get my hands on
enough money so that
I could live my dream.
I don't need a fortune.
My dream's a small one.
I wanna go to
another country where
I won't have to deal
with phonies anymore.
Maybe then I could meet a woman
who wouldn't call me a creep.
I could finally find
a little happiness.
Why can't a little dream
like mine come true?!
I've been a good
person up until today.
Am I doing something wrong?
What do you think, huh?
I...I don't know
Do you have a dream?
Yes, I do sir.
You think it'll come true?
I know it will...I'll
make it come true.
You're pretty sure
of yourself kid.
What's your dream?
I'm gonna create a Kaleido
Stage that will make
both the cast and
the audience smile.
Kaleido Stage?!
You mean you're part of
the Kaleido Stage cast?
That show's gotta be phony.
What?
What do you mean the
show's 'gotta be phony'?
Huh?
I can assure you that the
Kaleido Stage isn't fake.
I take it you're from the
Kaleido Stage too?
Well I'm not getting
drawn in by phonies!
Look, that stuff you
guys do is impossible,
and I'm not buying it.
Besides, I don't
believe anything
I haven't seen with my own eyes.
I'm a man with a heart of steel.
Then I'll just show you!
Show me what?
This isn't a good idea...
Don't do it Sora!
I'll give you a
performance right now!
Perform here?
This isn't the
time for that Sora!
You know he's right.
I'm talking to this
young lady about
dreams right now,
so quit butting in!
I'm gonna get angry!
So basically your dream is you
wanna make
everyone smile, right?
Yes.
Then why don't you
try and make me smile.
But remember, I've got
a heart made of steel.
I'll make you smile.
Woah, that's amazing!
I'm gonna borrow your rope.
Uh, sure.
Okay, I'm ready.
I hope that you enjoy
my performance.
Yeah.
Then my daughter's
boyfriend came in,
and do you know
what he called me?
Hey, what's going on?
What is it?
It looks like...
Like she's performing.
I wanna see! I wanna see!
I want to see! I want
to see! I want to see!
Mia, which bank is
it, I'm on my way!
I have to hurry or I'll miss it!
I've got an idea.
Is that supposed to be a smile?
That's all you've got?
Come in.
I thought I'd find ladies here.
I can't believe
you three have been
locked up in this room all week.
So what do you want?
Mia rang and said Sora's
got a role in a copper
drama for telly, and it's
filming at a local bank,
isn't that absolutely brill?
So, do you want
to go and watch it?
I have no idea what
she's talking about.
Let's go, I'm tired of
sitting around here.
Besides, we've done as much
as we possibly can today.
No fair, I'm trying
my best, I'll work harder!
Miss Layla...
Let's get out of here.
I'm right behind you.
You can come too May.
Oh Cathy, it's so lovely
of you to drive me there,
I assure you this
wasn't my intention
when I invited you along,
but cheers nonetheless!
Don't worry about it,
I really don't mind,
although it is a bit
cramped in here!
Right now this is my stage.
I'm gonna give it my all,
for all of the people who
are watching me,
including that man.
Sora!
Wow, that's so cool!
I guess it's a
real thing after all.
My friends helped me
remember what it's like
to be a part of the audience.
I remember I first fell in
love with Kaleido Stage
not because of the stunts,
but the fact that everyone on
stage looked like they were
having so much fun.
Once I understood that my
mom and dad were never
gonna come back, I started
thinking about Kaleido Stage
and how I wanted to
be a part of it.
I had so much fun when I saw the
show as little girl I thought
that maybe...if I was
part of Kaleido Stage,
I'd always be happy.
She's gonna fall!
I think I just saw you smile.
Looks like Sora
won your challenge.
Yeah, I guess she did.
Do you understand why
Sora did this performance?
I know she wanted to prove
to you and everyone
here that Kaleido
Stage isn't fake.
But she was determined to
help you get your smile back.
She wants to
see everyone smiling.
She loves to see people smile.
In fact all she wants
from her audience
is for them to walk
away with a smile.
You know, I wanna create a
Kaleido Stage show where the
audience and the cast
can all enjoy themselves.
I like to make people smile.
I know that trying to
make everyone smile may
seem like a far-fetched dream.
But Sora thinks she can do it.
That's why she works so hard.
For her dream?
She's inspired me to try working
toward my own little dream.
And what is that?
I'm gonna ask that beautiful
woman to marry me.
So, as you can see my dream's
not much bigger than yours.
Mine's not really a dream.
I'm just a loser looking
for a place to escape.
Why don't you start
over from the beginning?
Yeah, I just may do that.
Well then...
Don't worry,
I'll give myself up outside.
Besides, you've got something
more important to catch than me.
Hey, you can stop, I get it!
I take back what
I said about it being fake.
I'm sorry I ever said that.
Really?
It's been real fun.
Thanks a lot!
I hope that you'll come to see
the show at Kaleido Stage!
Sure, see you in five to seven!
It's over already?
What a shame.
That was such an
amazing performance,
we really lucked out!
That was amazing Sora!
That was so great!
Sora's always so
much fun to watch.
I hate to say it,
but her moves were great.
She wasn't even on stage.
What is it about her?
And why don't I have it?
Oh it's no big deal,
thanks a lot you guys!
Kinda feels like when we
were kids, doesn't it?
Yeah, Wonder Kate had to save
Crybaby Jerry every
time he got bullied.
That's why I started bulking up,
I didn't like being
seen as a weakling.
But your best feature has always
been your kindness, Jerry.
I...um, Kate?
What is it?
Kate!
I wanna put you
under eternal arrest!
This is for you.
Happy thirtieth birthday.
And as far as eternal arrest,
all I have to say is...yes.
Kate!
Way to go Mr. Policeman!
I guess that right
now the stage is the
only things that can
captivate Sora's heart.
What Sagittarius desires,
a stage with no competition
and colored with smiles,
is a foolish dream that
seems improbable.
It is so foolish it's a path
no one dares to walk.
What awaits her at the end?
Thunderous applause?
Or scornfulness.
Only one of the two.
What is this feeling that's
taken over me all of a sudden?
In the end, everyone
needs a chance to smile.
It may hurt, but I've
got to figure out;
what is it that Sora's
got that I don't?
Mr. Kenneth has demanded
that I perform with May!
And guess what?
Rosetta's gonna be there too!
I'm ready teacher!
Next time on Kaleido Star:
"Launching an Amazing Smile"!
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky.