We're about to raise
Kaleido Stage's curtain.
Remember that while you're
watching Kaleido Star,
you should keep
your room brightly lit
and sit as far from
the TV as you can.
I finally realized the one
thing I forgot to take care of.
It's the reason my heart is
pounding and it won't slow down.
I'm not her fellow
troupe member anymore.
Nor am I her partner.
I stand before her as a rival.
I've come back.
Give me your best shot, Sora!
My name is Layla.
Layla Hamilton,
the Golden Phoenix!
The competition is on, Sora.
And if you don't like it,
you'd better step down.
You said that you're going to
practice up until opening day.
That you'll make the true
Kaleido Star a reality.
Well I've been working
just as hard as you have.
And I'm not going to
give up without a fight.
The reason I entrusted my dream
to you is because I thought
you had something I didn't.
After all this time you still
haven't figured that out.
I've worked hard to master
the "Angel's Maneuver".
And I'm ready
to compete with you.
I'm sure you consider me
a worthy opponent.
If you chose to
decline my challenge,
then you're nothing but a loser.
If you honestly believe that
you can be a true Kaleido Star,
you'll have to
get through me first.
Sora.
Compete with Layla for a role?
My blood is racing
just thinking about it.
Why?
Why can't I hold back
my desire to challenge her?
I like the fire in your eyes.
I take it you're
up for the fight?
I am.
I'll see you tomorrow.
"A Most Amazing and
Inescapable Showdown."
One, two three.
Don't you think
it's kind of strange?
Huh?
What do you mean?
Nobody's talking about
the audition tomorrow.
Everyone's business as usual.
It's almost like they don't
care who gets the lead.
Maybe everyone likes
both of them equally.
I mean when you think about it,
it's not our decision.
So there's really nothing we
can but go about our business.
Quit thinking about who
will be playing the lead.
It's not going to change
your performance.
You have to give your role
everything you've got.
You don't have to tell me that.
I already know.
I know it will be difficult
with the time and
budget we have, but...
This is it Kalos,
it's perfect for the show!
It's your decision.
If you want to do it I'll start
working on it right away.
I'll have to tear
down the old set.
Alright, let's do it.
Awesome!
But if we're going to do it,
then it has to be perfect.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me, boss.
If I wanna debut as a clown,
I have to master this trick.
How many times has it been?
It seems like a thousand.
She's really putting everything
she's got into this show.
I can do this!
Anna?
Okay that's enough, Anna!
You're gonna hurt yourself!
I'm okay you guys.
I think I'll get
the hang of it soon.
I think we should stop here.
You need to get plenty of rest.
Yeah.
I thought for sure
you were going to refuse
to compete with her.
Yeah... I guess
that goes against
everything I've stood for.
But I... I can't
hold back my feelings.
Layla's the one who
taught me about the kindness
and the cruelty of the stage.
She was always
so far ahead of me.
She became a goal
that I could strive for.
Now she's come back
to the stage as my rival.
She left the Kaleido Stage
because of a shoulder injury.
It must have been so
painful for her to master
the "Angel's Maneuver".
She's so strong.
That's why I wanna
compete against her.
To show her I'm strong too.
Layla's very special to me,
she's taught me so much.
Then I guess meeting Layla
was the luckiest thing
that ever happened to you.
Yeah.
Sophie and I... we never
had that kind of luck.
In fact, I was
bad luck for Sophie.
I was the one who tied her down.
Let all her
potential go to waste.
And in order to atone,
I continued to go on stage.
I destroyed my partners...
in search of a True Star.
I've committed
so many wrongs, Sora.
If a True Star is born,
I can die satisfied.
Leon!
And so Leo turns
its fangs to Sagittarius.
Its brilliance increased
to a ferocious level.
Why did you come all this way?
Are you worried?
Both constellations
shine intensely.
However, their fate
is that if they collide,
one must disappear.
Is that so?
I thought my constellation
had already disappeared.
I should have known better.
Ever since the day I realized
I could still see you,
I wondered what it meant.
I knew it had
something to do with Sora.
I thought maybe I had
been chosen to guide her.
But in the end,
it was my actions that
caused her to take a detour.
Watching Sora regain her
brilliance, I had a realization.
I've never been allowed
to leave this stage behind.
So why shouldn't I return?
Just like May, after
Leon damaged her shoulder.
I can become a demon.
And if I do, it's possible
this demon could destroy
the true Kaleido Star
and all of her dreams.
Tomorrow, we shall see.
What a day!
I haven't been this
excited in a long time.
I've got butterflies
in my stomach.
It's strange.
I know it's a competition,
but there's none of the pain
that there was at the festival.
It's the opposite.
I'm happy I can compete.
You'll have to
get through me first.
Sora.
I'll do my best,
and I'll have no regrets.
But... Leon.
We have an important
audition going on today.
Let's try not to get
in the middle of it.
Now, time to start eating!
But Chinese food
for breakfast is...
You'd better start eating
and gather up your strength,
or she's gonna crush you!
She's gonna what?!
You don't wanna be
a pathetic loser, Sora.
You... think I'll lose?
That's beside the point.
I'm looking forward to seeing
Layla's "Angel Maneuver"...
but I'm looking forward
to yours as well.
Thank you.
Now hurry up and start chomping,
eat like you've
never eaten before!
You're not eating fast enough!
It's spicy!
Now some of this!
Too hot!
What about this?
It stinks!
The "Angel's Maneuver" requires
innate instinct and skill.
I'm impressed you mastered
it to this degree, Layla.
I had to perfect it,
or this competition
would be meaningless.
I wonder when it was.
What?
The last time that
I felt this feeling.
Maybe it was the first time
I stood on the Kaleido Stage.
Or maybe it was my first
audition for a leading role.
What about the first time you
completed the "Golden Phoenix"?
Those feelings seem
different somehow.
Yuri, my heart is racing; I'm so
excited about today's audition.
I guess we'll know soon.
Yeah.
So tell me.
Do you really think your
dream of a true Kaleido Star
will become a reality today?
Nobody knows for sure.
Hey Kalos.
What?
I like your socks.
I've always loved
your fashion sense, darling.
Let's go.
This is exciting.
What will happen?
Do you think Sora will be able
to fulfill our dreams, Kalos?
I have high hopes for her, sir.
And I've got high hopes
for her as well.
You know, I've been
told there's a door...
that only dreamers can open.
Scene 32.
The Angel's Flight.
It's finally gonna happen!
Yeah.
Leon?
What?
I think you're
wrong about Sophie.
You treasured her
above everything else.
And I'm sure that she felt
the same way about you.
You may not have
had anything else,
but you always had each other.
I think that having someone
to care about is happiness.
I know she was
happy because of you.
And I know that if I were
Sophie, I would never wanna
watch you suffer trying
to make up for the past.
You should be on stage
because you love it,
not because you're
atoning for the past.
If the stage brings you pain,
then you shouldn't go out there.
I'm sure I can do
this audition by myself.
If you're going on stage,
do it for your own sake.
For my own sake?
Let's go out there together and
get the biggest applause we can.
Let's show them
a real "Angel's Maneuver".
The biggest applause?
On stage with you, Sora?
I'd like that.
It's about to start.
Yes.
If I keep going straight down,
I should hit trapeze A-2.
I can feel it.
I can tell that I'm lined up
with trapeze A-5.
Yes!
They're both perfect.
On a technical level
they're completely equal.
True.
But, Sora's Odette
is lively and vivacious.
While Layla's Odette projects
an air of innocence.
Layla's so impressive!
To think, after all this time
she still has hidden talents
to show us.
This competition
could go either way.
They're both amazing,
aren't they?
There's so much
tension in the air.
Yeah, I'm kinda having
trouble breathing.
I'm proud of you, Sora.
Coming this far.
But now you have to create your
own path with your own power.
You're the first person
I've ever been able to
compete with on an equal level.
I can feel your
passion for the stage.
Back then, I never dreamed
a day like this would come.
The first time I saw you
perform I was so frustrated.
So angry.
But now...
Someday the audience
will come to Kaleido Stage
just to see her perform.
Kalos...
It's just like you said.
Actually, she overcame each
ordeal with more strength
than you'd ever imagined.
She became my partner.
And now, she's my rival.
Sora.
I want nothing more
than to defeat you.
When Layla's on stage,
her energy makes the
air crackle with tension.
Her drive to defeat me
makes me even stronger.
I can't lose my focus,
or I'll lose.
I can't afford
to make any mistakes.
My "Angel's Maneuver" will
awaken everyone's angel hearts.
I have to perform
my "Angel's Maneuver"!
Wait a minute,
I just had a great idea.
I'm gonna do a little loopy loo.
I'll follow.
That's not what
was choreographed.
The "Angel's Maneuver" will
awaken everyone's angel hearts.
Even my own... angel heart.
The people who gave me my angel
heart, all four of my parents,
and even Yume.
Everyone has people who
are important to them.
Maybe our angel hearts are
treasures that are given to us
by the people we care about.
Sora has started
ad-libbing her performance.
I can't say that I'm surprised.
Layla is seriously
trying to beat Sora.
She may be performing
the "Angel's Maneuver",
but she's as
relentless as a demon.
The demon that raises an angel.
That was Layla all along.
The one who wants
Sora to surpass.
Or the one who wants
to defeat Sora.
Which façade is the real you?
Or, are they both the real you?
Your performance is so peaceful.
It's hard to believe
you're fighting for a role.
Could it be...?
The performers and the
audience will become one.
You want to perform on that
kind of stage, don't you Leon?
I wonder why... the audience
is suddenly so calm.
What in the world is going on?
There's something strange
about Layla's angel.
I wonder why...
I just remembered
my grandmother.
When I was a little girl,
I used to write stories and
then read them to my grandma.
I remember how she smiled.
She always said she really
enjoyed story-time.
I was just thinking
about when I was a child,
I made a picture book for
a sick friend of mine.
It was horrible, but somehow
it made her feel better.
I wonder why...
For some reason I just thought
about my first diabolo show.
I screwed up a little,
but someone in the front row
clapped for me and told me
that I was amazing.
I remember telling my mother
jokes whenever she cried.
Doing anything
to make her laugh.
She didn't think
they were funny,
but I always got her
to smile again.
I remember asking mama
to teach me how to play
on the trampoline.
Mama... she was so happy.
Why did this just
pop into my head?
It's got nothing to do
with skating or Kaleido Stage.
I remember teaching my little
brothers wrestling moves.
May Wong Devil Headhang!
Once I started skating lessons,
I didn't get to play
with them anymore.
The room... it's so warm...
The audience is
completely tranquil.
Eerily calm.
Is it because of Sora?
I can't remember the
last time I felt this feeling.
I remember.
It was that day.
The day my mother and father
rearranged their busy schedules
to bring me to Kaleido Stage
for the first time.
I was so excited about
everything happening onstage.
That's the feeling
of an audience member.
On the way here I realized
I was looking forward
to Sora's performance.
I want to see her
"Angel's Maneuver".
An angel.
That was amazing!
Wow!
It seems the decision
has been made, Layla.
Yes, Mr. Kenneth.
Sora.
Uh, yes?
They say a true prima has the
ability to turn their costars
into spectators.
While competing, I couldn't
help but watch you.
I became an audience member.
I simply couldn't hold back
my desire to see your
"Angel's Maneuver".
You've become the performer
I could never be.
I'm proud of you, Sora.
Layla I...
Sora, now that you've
arrived at the gates
of true Kaleido Stardom, there's
something I have to say.
Performers will be drawn here
by their admiration of you.
When that happens,
you must always meet
your challengers head on.
And when your time is up,
you must fight with
all your strength
to accept defeat.
Competing with your challengers
will be a duty of yours.
Don't forget that.
You see, that's the
one thing I forgot to do
before I left this stage.
It's what I hoped
to accomplish today.
I left the stage
without being defeated.
And because of that I never
really felt independent.
Sora, competing with
your challengers will be
another important duty
of yours from now on.
Don't forget that.
Okay.
Congratulations Sora.
Thank you for everything.
The results of the audition
have been decided.
There are only a few days
until opening day,
so everyone start practicing!
Yes sir!
Until your wishes come true,
you're not alone.
I cried a lot.
I laughed a lot.
I was really frustrated.
I was really happy.
We've all felt so many
different emotions.
I'm so glad you've take
this journey with us.
This is what happens when
you chase your dreams!
The final episode
of Kaleido Star,
"To The Amazing Promised Place"!
My wings are my dream,
okay everyone!
And on toward the sky!