We're about to raise the
curtain on Kaleido Star.
As you watch the show, make
sure your room is brightly lit
and that you're not sitting
too close to the television.
Well, well, well.
Has anyone out there gotten
to the point where you say
to yourself, 'I just
can't do this anymore?'
You work so hard, but then you
hit your limit and it looks like
you'll never be able
to get what you want.
But then a friend comes along
who really believes in you.
And encourages you to be better
than you thought you could be.
I'm so glad, so glad!
I'm going down to the
river to do some laundry.
Okay.
Charlotte? Julie?
You guys are here too?
Uh, yeah...
I haven't seen
you two in a while.
How come you're not
at Kaleido Stage?
Did you quit or something?
Let's just say we had a little
disagreement with Yuri.
And when he overheard
that he fired us.
Shhh!
How's Sora?
Working hard, as usual?
'Working hard' is
a huge understatement.
Yeah, she looks awful.
Her training regimen's
extremely severe.
If I had to work
as hard as that I'd die!
I just don't know
how she can endure it.
I've got a lot of
respect for her.
What has Sora gotten
herself into this time?
'The Amazing Intensive
Training Continues.'
Yes, we're very excited about
their attempt so we've planned
countdown events
leading up to the show.
I want Layla and Sora
to have a packed house.
Well, you're
creating quite a buzz,
so I don't think
you have to worry.
But why the decision to make
tickets nonrefundable even if
they can't complete the
Legendary Great Maneuver?
Well, as you know, a few
months ago when Kaleido Stage
changed hands we had to cancel a
few performances of 'Freedom.'
That created some
financial strain.
I don't mean to
malign my predecessor,
but Kaleido Stage was
in a state of disarray.
From my perspective, I think
it's only fair that people know
what they're getting into
when they purchase a ticket,
especially considering how
difficult this trick is.
And how have your
ticket buyers reacted?
Not a single complaint.
There is a rumor that your
father was part of the last
Kaleido Stage team to attempt
the Legendary Great Maneuver.
That's right. And my
father never succeeded with
the maneuver, he died
during a rehearsal.
So this is an extremely
dangerous stunt?
Yes, it's going to be very
difficult, and that's why
we want to give Layla
and Sora so much support.
Best of luck to them.
We'll be showing a live
broadcast of their attempt
of the Legendary Great
Maneuver next month.
So are they going to be able to
pull this thing off or what?
That's pretty doubtful.
I'm about 99% sure we'll
have to cancel this show.
That show sold out within
minutes of our announcement.
And now all the countdown
shows are selling out, too.
It seems like people really
want to see this thing.
Who knew they'd
care so much about
the Legendary Great Maneuver?
I know it's a huge draw so I've
got a plan to keep our momentum
going after the cancellation.
Layla and I are going to
announce our attempt at--
That won't be necessary.
Once you cancel we can
end Kaleido Stage.
It'll be the perfect chance
for us to sell it off.
Sell it?
You didn't think we'd just stand
by while you ran this place
into the ground, did you?
That old coot Kenneth saw
this coming from a mile away.
I should've
bailed out when he did.
Again!
Sora!
Oh Mia, Anna. I didn't
know you were coming.
How's Jonathan and
everyone in Cape Mary?
You don't need to
make small talk with us.
What's going on here?
This is my special training.
Special training? What?
Ken, how could you
do this to Sora?
Come on, stand up.
You've got to keep working
if you want to
catch up with Layla.
Yes. You're right.
But Sora...
This is foolish.
I know, and being foolish
is my my specialty--
Sora!
Ken, you can't work her
any more today.
We're taking her to the lodge.
Okay.
I understand she's gotta train,
but for her to be so
bruised-- it's ridiculous.
I can't believe Ken? I thought
he'd at least try to protect
her from this kind of thing.
Oh no!
I overslept. I've got to train!
Where are you going?
You can train, but
you need to rest first!
Calm down, Sora!
If you don't take a break,
you're going to kill yourself.
You're working too hard.
I appreciate your concern, but
I'm fine now and I've got to go.
Layla's training is already
more intense than mine,
and I don't wanna
be left behind.
Sora!
Even Layla looks like
she's being beaten
down by this training.
The Legendary Great Maneuver...
I knew it would be difficult,
but I never would've guessed
in a hundred years
that it'd be like this.
Do you think we should
tell her what we found out?
Hmm.
'Cause I kind of think she'd
be better off not knowing.
You could be right...
You did it!
I did it...
That's useless if you can't
repeat it. We'll be out here
until you can do it
ten times in a row.
All right.
Are you ready?
Yes!
I think I'm beginning
to understand just what
the Legendary Great
Maneuver entails.
It would be incredible if I
could do it but as long as
there's such a gulf
between me and Sora,
I know it'll never work.
Layla, you can't be finished
with dinner already.
Yes. I'm afraid I don't
have much of an appetite.
Starting tomorrow, I'd like
to eat meals in my room.
Uh... sure.
I wonder...
That's ten!
Okay, now we can move on
to the next training level.
Let's get started.
I want to earn
the kind of applause
that makes my
whole body tremble!
I have been doing
a lot of thinking.
Sora I know we can do this.
No matter what happens, we've
got to be at that performance...
Right!
Just keeping my body
rigid is going to be hard,
and that's only the half of it.
Swinging that high is...
Are you gonna work or what?
Yes, sir!
I don't know, Layla seems
a little irritated to me.
I wonder if that's why
she doesn't want
to eat at the table.
It could be,
but maybe she just doesn't
like Charlotte's cooking.
Take that back! Right now!
No, I don't think that's it.
Yeah, your food's
actually pretty good.
Thank you, Anna. It's nice
that someone appreciates me...
Maybe Layla's upset because she
thinks I'm not good enough.
I wonder... I wonder if
I have what it takes to be
her partner after all.
Her stability has improved
a lot over the last week.
But it's like she's lost
her motivation somehow...
I can't watch anymore.
You wanna go give
Charlotte and Julie a hand?
Layla, wait. Tell me
what I'm doing wrong.
Tell me to work harder,
be stronger.
How I can be a better partner.
Or tell me I'll never be good
enough to work with you anyway.
Just please say something.
Please talk to me, Layla!
Tell me what I've done
that's so terrible!
Sora... I'm sorry,
I have nothing to say.
Mr. Kenneth?
What's he doing here?
I hope nothing's wrong.
Uh, to bring you
all the way out here...
Your face looks like
you've aged thirty years
in just ten days, Sora.
What became of that competitive
spirit? Your eyes are empty now.
You don't look like
someone capable of doing
the Legendary Great Maneuver.
Sora's just exhausted because
she's been training all d--
Looks like all this is going to
turn out just like they wanted.
What are you talking about?
All those maggots who've
still got their money
in Kaleido Stage, that's what.
They don't believe
you can do it.
And, as a matter of fact,
they're hoping you'll fail.
Whether you can perfect
the maneuver or not,
they'll still get their money.
And, after all, that's
really all they care about.
But that's...
Actually, they'd be happiest
of all if the show
was canceled altogether.
That way, they
don't have to worry
about the show-day expenses.
But what about the audience?
What about them? Can you
even tell me with certainty
you won't disappoint them?
That you and Layla will
succeed at this thing?
Can you look me in the eye and
say 'I'm not going to fail?'
I...
Can you even say you deserve
to be a partner to
the great Layla Hamilton?
Tell me to work
harder, be stronger.
How I can be a better partner.
Or tell me I'll never be good
enough to work with you anyway.
Just please say something.
Please talk to me, Layla!
Tell me what I've
done that's so terrible!
I'm sorry, I have
nothing to say.
I...
Sora!
I don't know what your angle is,
saying something
like that to her,
but she's having
a tough enough time trying
to keep her spirits up without
you knocking her down.
It's nice out here. I think
I'll stay a little while.
Wha--? Stay here?
Make me a coffee,
will you, Chauncey?
That's not my name.
It's Ken Robbins.
Sora?
Why couldn't I say it?
Why couldn't I just
tell him I can do this?
That I have it in me?
I guess I let it go to my head,
being partners with Layla,
and now I'm finding out
that I just don't...
I just don't have what
it takes to be on stage
with her after all.
And when Mr. Kenneth said
that all I could think to do
was run away, I--
I couldn't answer him.
You can't beat yourself up
about that, Sora.
But you know,
if you want to quit none of us
will think any less of you.
I'm sure Layla would understand
if you explained it to her.
No, she wouldn't. You should
have heard what she said to me:
Doubting yourself
is just a waste of time.
Either do this or don't try.
But it might be the best thing
for Layla if I let her choose
a more talented partner...
It's very kind of you to come
all this way just to see us.
Yep. But I was mostly interested
in seeing Sora's progress,
since she's such
a talented girl.
I never would've dreamed
she'd be good enough to attempt
the Legendary Great
Maneuver, though.
I wouldn't have, either.
They're the first
since Arlon Brass, huh?
That's right.
You're still blaming yourself
for Arlon's stupidity,
aren't you?
I was partly
responsible after all.
Well. Arlon Brass
was a good man,
but he had no business
attempting that maneuver.
And, as I recall,
you told him so several times.
What?
It's true, Arlon Brass
was one of the last people
to attempt the maneuver
at Kaleido Stage.
If his name sounds familiar
it's because he was a top star
at the time, and he's
also Yuri's father.
And Jean confirmed what
Mia heard, so it's all true.
Yuri must have told his
investors exactly what happened
last time so naturally
they don't believe
the Legendary Great
Maneuver can be done.
It has nothing
to do with you, Sora.
I see.
It's a deal. So you've
got exactly one month
to perfect this
Legendary Great Maneuver.
He only made that bet because he
thought we'd never be able to do
the Legendary Great Maneuver and
win Kaleido Stage back from him.
Seems to me your biggest
problem's is not Sora's
physical capabilities. The
great challenge is getting Sora
to believe in herself.
Well, if she doesn't believe
in herself at least that means
she won't be foolish enough
to try the maneuver anyway.
I suppose you have
a point there.
Still, I don't think we should
sell these young people short.
They come up with amazing
things when their backs
are to the wall.
My money's on Sora.
Is that why you took your
money out of Kaleido Stage:
you like the thrill
of the unknown?
Well, I guess that's part of it.
I just couldn't stand doing
business with those maggots.
I'm taking Layla
her tray, all right?
Fine.
Sora's not coming; she doesn't
have much of an appetite.
We should probably leave her be.
Right.
Yes?
What is it?
Well, it's just that...
Layla told me not to say
anything about this, but I
thought that you should know.
Layla? I need to talk
to you. Can I come in?
Ken.
Layla isn't in her room right
now. She went out for a run.
She's gone running?
But it's not light yet.
Layla's trying
to lose some weight.
But why?
Because when you perform the
Legendary Great Maneuver
you have a much higher
chance of success
if both partners
weigh roughly the same.
I guess Layla looked at
the training and figured out
what kind of trick
this is gonna be.
She should probably
be back any time now.
You know how Layla's been eating
all of her meals in her room
for the past few days?
Well, it turns out she's not
eating much of anything.
What?
Charlotte told me
about it last night.
I guess Layla wanted her
to keep it a secret.
But that's so dangerous. And
she's doing this because of me?
Well, Sora, you're trying to
be a better partner for Layla.
It's only fair she should try
to be a better partner for you.
You need to stop believing
that all the problems in this
partnership are your fault.
I mean, aren't the two of
you supposed to be equal?
So Layla is...
I idolized her
for such a long time.
It's true, you have
something I don't possess.
This has to be a real fight
between the two of us.
When I was a little
girl I came to see
one of their shows
with my parents.
It was wonderful, just
like a beautiful dream.
Don't think that means I'll
never be able to perform again.
This isn't my last show
unless I choose for it to be.
I've never, not once
in all these years,
had a partner that's
motivated me this much.
Layla...
I always thought the two of
you were perfectly matched.
Thanks for saying that Ken.
Layla!
Sora?
I'm so sorry. I wanted to run
away because training's so hard.
I told myself I didn't have
what it takes to be
your partner, anyway.
But I'm not gonna
doubt myself anymore,
and I'm gonna work extra
hard to catch up with you
so we can perfect the maneuver
and get Kaleido Stage back.
And I promise, Layla,
I won't doubt myself again.
I'll work twice as hard. I'll
be the partner you deserve--
the partner you're
trying to be for me.
No matter what it takes,
I'm not going to let you down.
We're going to do the
Legendary Great Maneuver!
I've never doubted for a moment
that you and I would be able
to do this thing.
Right.
But I don't want you to lose any
more weight for this, all right?
I'll eat more, I'll gain weight,
I'll get stronger, anything.
Sounds good to me.
That's the girl we've
been waiting to see.
Then I'm glad you came out, sir.
I knew this would be worth
every second of the drive.
I tell you, she must be tough
to claw her way out
of such despair.
You mean you
planned all this? But--
Well, now that I'm awake,
I could use a nice
stiff bourbon, young boy.
My name is Ken Robbins.
And from now on I think
I'd like it if we didn't
keep secrets from each other.
Good idea.
Then it's settled.
Not yet. You're still not
qualified to know about
the Legendary Great Maneuver.
The inverted Empress. It seems
that fate has even more ordeals
in store for the two of you.
If you overcome this adversity,
there's no way
that you can fail.
But your success may come
at the greatest price of all.
Only time will tell...
What happened?
Did you hurt yourself?
It's nothing, I'm fine.
I thought I just saw
you hit your shoulder.
I just wasn't concentrating
and scratched it a little bit.
It's all right.
I think you should go get it
checked out, just in case.
We don't have time for that,
Sora. Come on.
Let's get back to work.
Right.
I guess it's no big deal.
She's doing fine.
Losing that weight
took it out of me.
I passed out for a second.
This injury's not going
to ruin our chances.
I just need it to
last a little longer.
She's crying!
It's the day before
our performance,
and Layla's injuries are worse
than even she could've imagined.
But even in the face of that,
she's still determined to go on.
Why has she kept this
from us for so long?
And why does she push herself
so hard? Why? Why? Why?
Make sure not to miss our next
episode, 'An Amazing Bond.'
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...