Everybody, Kaleido Star
is about to start!
You're gonna want to make sure
that your room is brightly lit
and that you're not sitting
too close to the TV.
Is everyone ready?
Yep!
Well, well, well.
Have you ever been really
determined to do something?
I mean, so determined that you
won't let anyone or anything
sway you from your goal?
I've tried lots
of things in my life,
and I've always done my best,
but now it looks like I'll be
facing my biggest challenge yet.
It kinda scares me,
but there's no way I'm gonna
back down now! No way! No way!
What's this...
This?!
Can you see me now, Layla?
'The Legendary
Amazing Maneuver.'
Where are we-- Sora!
What's gotten into you?
You saw him! You're able
to see the Fool now too!
Well I saw something...
That's right, the Fool.
He has a name?
What Sora neglected to mention
is I'm the spirit of the stage.
Amazing. I wasn't that calm
when I saw him the first time.
Oh, baby, that tickles.
Well, I'm glad that
you can see him too,
then I'm not just
losing my mind here.
Believe me, if anybody's
insane it's him.
Hey!
But Layla does this mean you
couldn't see him before today?
Layla has always been a capable
performer in the past...
But today you've proven
to be more than that,
and now you're worthy
of all my secrets.
What kind of secrets?
The Legendary Great Maneuver.
No one's attempted it in years
and the last person who did paid
for the privilege with his life.
But he was not the first to
fall. Many tried before him,
and many failed.
If you ladies try this,
you will only be the second team
from Kaleido Stage to do so.
The second?
Yes. It is very rare that I
find two stars capable of it.
What happened to the other
team from Kaleido Stage?
They died.
It turns out one of the partners
couldn't see me at all.
He just pretended to.
So I was tricked into
revealing my secret.
But Layla really can see you!
And I've seen you for ages.
So that means you're going to
tell us how to do it, right?
Not right now.
That would be a mistake.
I'll reveal the maneuver to you
when you're
qualified to perform it.
Qualified?
How can we prepare if we don't
know what we're aiming for?
You'll have to figure
that out on your own.
In the meantime,
I think I've said enough.
Don't be mean! C'mon, tell us!
Sora, if you were to try
that maneuver now...
The Death card.
Surely one of you
would die. Maybe both.
But I know... I know
I could do it with you...
that we could do it together!
I'm going to have
to think about this.
But Layla, I promise I'll
try my best! I promise...
She doesn't think
I'm good enough.
It looks like Layla's gonna
be a part of the troupe now.
Yes.
So if she leaves London
first thing in the morning,
she can be here by noon.
I mean, with the time
difference and all.
I've gotta do it-- I've gotta
convince her somehow to try
the Legendary Great Maneuver.
The legendary what now?
What's that, Sora?
I don't know. But now that
Layla's my gonna be my partner,
I know that whatever it is we
can do it if we both want to.
I just have to convince her...
Come one, come all to the
brand-new Kaleido Stage!
You won't want to miss the
amazing special effects!
Come on, step right up
ladies and gents!
Hey, Julie, did you hear? The
masked star was Layla after all.
Man, I wish I was
in that company.
I know. I'm starting to think
I'd rather be a bit player
in Layla's show
than a star here.
But I guess you don't
have that choice.
Neither do I, for that matter.
I bet if Layla was here
our audiences wouldn't just keep
getting smaller and smaller--
If you don't
like it you can leave.
You're released
from your duties.
But we-- We got fired!
I think it's for the best.
It's Yuri.
Did you hear? Kaleido Stage
is about to go under...
I'm glad you agreed to meet me.
How did the rest of filming go?
It went very well thank you.
Good, I'm glad to hear that.
Is that why you asked me here?
I want you to come back Layla.
Kaleido Stage just isn't
the same without you there.
I want us to perform
as partners again.
I already have a
partner, Yuri. It's Sora.
The two of us have even been
talking about attempting
the Legendary Great Maneuver.
That's crazy. You can't
do that with Sora.
She's a beginner for
God's sake! You can't do this!
I've decided.
Well, if you're gonna do it,
you should do it with me!
You are not qualified.
I see.
When I saw Kaleido Stage
for the first time it was like
some kind of wonderful dream.
I wished I was part
of the show, too.
About a year after my
parents died I started
taking gymnastic classes.
It was fun for me,
and I was good at it.
That was the first time
I got applause.
I remember just starting out,
working on this
difficult maneuver.
And when I perfected it,
the applause made me tremble.
It was such an amazing
feeling to be on stage for
the first time and
to hear people cheering.
That's why I push
myself to be the best.
That's why I always want more.
I wanna show them.
I want them to see it.
That's why we've got to try. We
can do this Layla, I know it!
The Legendary Great Maneuver?
I'm sure Kalos would
know something about it.
Or at least about the
people who've attempted
the maneuver before.
I see. But he might not
want to discuss it.
It's been years since he's said
anything about that routine.
Even if Sora and I
want to give it a try?
I suppose he'll want to
tell you everything he can.
I'll give you his
contact information.
Oh no! I just had
my back turned for a second.
Master, would you mind
showing me that again?
Could you wait for
a moment, Layla?
Sure.
You never stop training,
do you, Sora?
I can't afford to take any
time off. Not if I want to be
good enough to
perform with Layla.
Sora, is this true?
What?
'Layla Hamilton and Sora Naegino
will return to Kaleido Stage
for one night only to attempt
a deadly trick known only as
the "Legendary Great Maneuver."'
Really?
The show's next month.
Oh no.
Can I help you with something?
Yes, there was an announcement
in the news today about
the Legendary Great Maneuver?
Oh, I'm sorry, miss.
That show's already sold out.
What?!
Hey, you can't go back there.
I'm one of the
performers in that show!
Huh?
Good morning, Sora.
Yuri.
Well, your little show
sold out in minutes.
But if you want some comps
for your friends and family,
I'm sure we could arrange
something for you and Layla--
But how did you know
we were going to try this?
I heard it from Layla.
Do you mean that Layla
told you she wanted to try
the Legendary Great Maneuver?
But Yuri made the announcement
without consulting us.
So, what? You're trying
to humiliate us?
On the contrary, I'm paying
you both a great compliment.
Not everyone is qualified
to perform this maneuver.
It's just my luck there are
two qualified performers
who want to attempt it.
But if you two are getting
cold feet we might as well
cancel the show right now.
It's too bad the tickets
aren't refundable.
But you--
We're not going to cancel.
And I think we should make
the stakes a little higher.
What do you mean?
If we successfully
perform the maneuver,
you will return
Kaleido Stage to Kalos.
It's a deal. So you've got
exactly one month to perform
this Legendary Great Maneuver.
Layla?
I've been doing
a lot of thinking.
Sora I know we can do this.
No matter what happens, we've
got to be at that performance
and we've got to win.
We will work on this stage again
and it's not going
to be for just one night.
Right. But Layla, how can
we prepare for this if
we don't even know
what we'll be doing?
Kalos will tell us
what we need to do.
He's helping?
I think he's the
only one who can.
He told me he remembers how the
last group from Kaleido Stage
prepared for this. We can
meet him at the Grand Canyon.
That is, if you want to Sora.
Of course I do.
And he really said he'd
give Kaleido Stage back?
Yes, as long as Layla and I
can do the maneuver perfectly.
We're gonna do our best to get
Kaleido Stage back for everyone!
And the Boss is gonna coach you?
We know you can do it, Sora.
Me and Jonathan
believe in you, too.
We're gonna be there
to cheer you on.
I bought tickets as soon as I
heard you'd be on stage, Sora.
I'm going with you.
What?
Kalos is going to work you
to the bone out there.
You'll need a trainer, Sora.
Ken.
Hey, I wanna go, too!
And so do I!
Why don't we all go together?
But that's impossible...
So the Boss is going to
tell us how to train for
the Legendary Great Maneuver.
Just keep in mind, if you
find out what the trick is
before you're
prepared to do it--
I know, I know.
I already saw the Death card.
Hey, we came along
to help you train.
Aren't you a lucky girl?
Uh. I guess so...
Sora. I came along because
I support your decision
to do this. But if--
If I ever think you're in real
danger I'm going to make you
give up on this. I think you
should know that up front.
Ken.
I don't want to
risk losing you, Sora.
It's been a while, huh? Welcome.
Hi, Boss.
Let's get to work.
I have a really bad
feeling about this...
What?
I've e-mailed everyone
I can find that used
to work at Kaleido Stage,
asking about the Legendary
Great Maneuver, you know.
I found out that the last
time anyone tried to do it
was ten years ago...
And what happened?
Both of them died.
I wonder who they were...
I've found another
recipe for you to try.
Let me know what you think
of this one first. Well?
That's really disgusting.
Then why don't you do
the cooking from now on?
'Cause I'm not
very good at this stuff.
Next, you'll do a hundred
one-armed chin-ups.
No resting!
Sora?
Now jump.
Oh no. Help!
Help!
That's it for today's training.
Not yet. Sora, I need you
to do a hundred curls
with your right hand.
You ready?
Yes.
I can cut that
for you if you want.
Thank you, Ken. I'll be okay.
I've gotta get used to this.
Yeah, you're right.
But-- that's impossible.
That maneuver can't be done.
He said that
in order to perfect it,
all someone would need
is absolute confidence.
Who said that?
But that doesn't just
apply to the two of them.
It applies to
everyone around them.
If you want Sora
and Layla to succeed,
you can never let them know
you have that any doubts.
You'll have to be relentless.
You can never let them stint
on their training. Never
If you can't do that,
you'd better leave right now.
But if you stay, you won't
tell Sora about the maneuver.
It hurts but you'll have to bear
it. If I don't loosen you up
you won't be able to train.
Tomorrow's gonna be
a lighter day than today,
but after that we're gonna--
Ken?
Do you-- do you really
think that I can do this?
I mean, if the
training's this hard,
how will I ever get through it?
Now she's doubting herself?
Good.
We've been doing
the same program
for more than a week now.
Don't complain.
Just do what Kalos says.
Ken, you you sound like
a different person.
And so do you, Sora.
Weren't you the one
who wanted to try
the Legendary Great Maneuver
in the first place?
I-- yes.
Layla, you've completed the
first level. You'll start
training on the ropes first
thing tomorrow morning.
Good.
Sora. Come here.
Sir.
The iron ball hanging
from this wire weighs
about as much as Layla.
What you have to do is catch
the ball with your right hand
and push it back to me.
If you can't do this,
you can't be Layla's partner.
Got it, Sora?
Yes. I'm ready, Boss!
If you want Sora
and Layla to succeed,
you can never let them
know you have any doubts.
Kalos, wait a minute!
What, Ken?
I would like to handle
this part of her training
if you don't mind.
You would?
Are you sure that
you're up to it?
I am.
Are you ready Sora?
Let's go.
Come on.
Sora. Stand up.
I'm ready.
Again!
I...I've gotta catch
that ball no matter what.
I've got to do the
Legendary Great Maneuver!
Stand up, Sora.
Resting's not gonna help.
I want you to stop this
thing before dinnertime.
I wish I knew what
I'm trying to achieve...
I wonder how long I can
keep going like this?
I just wish I knew what
all this is for. Fool?
Fool, where are you?
Will you tell me now?
Not yet.
But, Fool...
I told you before:
I'll let you know what the
maneuver entails only when
you're ready to perform it,
not a moment sooner.
So I'm still not good enough?
Not yet, not yet...
Can you even say you deserve
to be a partner to
the great Layla Hamilton?
I'm training harder than
ever before, but still--
This is ridiculous!
She's going to destroy herself!
I've got to keep training. I
don't want to give up, but...
Every day I feel like
crying or running away.
Layla, please say something
to me! Please! Please!
Don't miss the
next Kaleido Star,
'The Amazing Intensive
Training Continues.'
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...