Attention everyone.
Kaleido Star is about to begin.
While watching Kaleido
Star, keep your room lit
and sit away from the TV.
Right Miss!
Hey everyone!
Cathy here.
You kids don't know
how good you've got it.
When you're young it's easier
to push yourselves to extremes.
You can shoot for the stars!
For example, look at everyone
here at Kaleido Stage!
Everyone's determined
to achieve their dream.
Nothing can get in their way.
All this dream chasing is
making for one amazing show!
Alright, I'm getting revved up.
Hope you kids are ready
coz I'm sticking through
with you 'til the end!
I've changed my mind
about training.
We'll start again tomorrow.
Yes sir!
You need to get up.
We're wasting time.
Yes sir.
She must be sore
from those weights,
she's been training all day!
Do you want to take a break?
No.
Sora...
Why does she have to keep
training until she
collapses like that?
I have to... keep going.
"Our Amazing Futures."
Simon Park has agreed to write
Swan Lake's press release.
Hmm.
That's one problem fixed,
but what about Layla?
I've made it clear that I'm not
going to try and stop Layla.
You're a real piece of work.
A "Perfect Angel's Maneuver"
requires innate instinct.
What makes you think
that Layla has the strength
to pull this off, Kalos?
How will the audience react to
someone who suddenly comes back
to the stage to make
a second attempt at stardom?
She had a brilliant exit.
This could ruin her reputation!
Are you going to be
the one to tell her?
I'm certainly gonna try.
But, if she won't give up...
I'll just have to ruin my
reputation along with her.
So whaddya think?
During the performance,
I wanna use lasers in the
areas where I've put markers.
Well, I... I think the
design is pretty good,
but I feel like it's
missing something...
Just get to the point
and tell him it's no good.
Cathy!
I never said it was no good!
So you're saying it's good?!
Well no...
Then that means it's no good.
I guess so.
I see.
I'm sorry Jean.
There's no need
for you to apologize.
Yes there is,
we know who's at fault!
Yeah, I know, it's my fault.
I still haven't completely
worked out how we're going
to stage the climax of the show.
What are you gonna do?
We can't build the set
'til you figure it out.
I'll start working on it now.
That's my girl,
give it your best shot!
You can figure this thing out
if you keep working at it!
Keep working at it until
you collapse like Sora!
I'm gonna keep working at it
until I collapse like Sora!
She's right, I gotta keep going.
It all depends on me.
Wow, the seal really loved it.
Does that mean... its good?
I'm not really sure...
The only way Odile
can express her love
is through her hatred of Odette.
That means, if she
destroys Odette,
she wouldn't be able
to express her love again.
When Sora wasn't onstage,
I couldn't perform my best
because I had no one
to compete with.
I am Odile.
Odile's relationship with
the prince is like my
relationship with the stage.
Odile will never win the
prince's love as long as
she keeps trying
to defeat Odette.
The difference between
Odette and Odile...
Odile is obsessed with
winning the prince's affection,
and she won't let
anything stand in her way.
But Odette values her love
for the prince more than
she values herself, and
strives to make him happy.
Sora's love for the stage
is more important
to her than anything.
As long as I keep trying to
defeat Sora, I'll never win.
Pose number nine.
Yes sir!
You care more about the
stage than you do yourself.
That means she's
just like... Odette.
This special training seems
to get more and more
difficult every day.
Hello?
Can I come in?
Oh, hi!
I'll tell her you're here.
Miss Layla, Mr. Yuri's outside!
You can let him in.
Okay.
Sorry for the wait,
I'll be right there.
Thank you for waiting.
Come in.
Miss Layla is in the
practice room in the basement.
Thank you.
Why are you so stubborn?
If you're not
going to be my partner,
you might as well leave now.
I don't get it.
Attempting to make
a comeback is rough.
You'll either be praised
for your determination,
or you'll be laughed off stage.
They'll think you're trying
to steal the spotlight.
From... the people
you've left behind.
I don't care what anyone thinks.
I have to do this Yuri.
I don't have a choice.
So I guess you're too
exhausted to take a bath, huh?
Huh?
What's that?
What are you trying to say?
Did you say you want me
to help you get undressed?
Massage... will you... please?
How's this feel?
Am I going it right?
It's not helping.
Never mind.
Thanks though.
Ouch.
That really hurt.
You mean like this?
Hey, there's a bar
at the bottom!
That's for you to stand on.
Okay.
Sora, are you ready to begin?
Yeah!
Looks like this part of
training is gonna be harsh.
No matter what, you have to
maintain your pose on the bar.
Yes sir!
Hey Rosetta!
What is it?
I'm thinking about making
my move during the climax
a two-person maneuver.
Really?
I already talked
to Cathy about it.
Yeah?
You are so dense.
You're my partner, so we've
gotta start practicing.
Hold on a second!
I told you I wasn't gonna
be in the show, May!
I know.
But are you really
okay with that?
I made my decision.
I thought you were
as determined as Sora.
But I guess that
I was wrong about you.
Sora's determined to have
a brilliant performance
no matter what.
Even if it's her last one.
By the time I finally
made it to Kaleido Stage,
Miss Layla had already
left the troupe.
I was so sad and disappointed.
The maneuver I'm thinking about
can't be done by one person,
so I'm giving you
the chance I never had.
But if you don't want to do it,
I'll start looking
for someone else.
What'll you do?
If you wanna do this,
then I'll train you.
But just so you know,
it will be hard.
Alright.
I'll do it.
I'll be your partner, May.
Good decision.
Her balance has started
to improve a little.
But, she isn't comfortable
landing the pose.
The "Angel's Maneuver" still
isn't ready for the stage.
I don't know if Sora can survive
much more of this training.
That's it!
How about a little
change of scene?
Huh?
Cathy?
Where are we going
at this time of night?
You'll just have to wait
and see when we get there!
I guess the seal
really liked it, huh?
Yeah.
If only we could fill
the audience with seals.
Mia, take a look.
Yeah?
They're real swans!
You got it.
Mother Nature is
the best director.
Sometimes it's good for us to
sit back and be her audience.
You're right.
I thought seeing them may
help you picture your angel.
An angel that doesn't fight.
An angel who can forgive
the hatred in her heart.
I thought that Sora was
perfect for the role, but...
It's almost too perfect.
Yeah.
I mean, I know that sounds
weird since I wrote it.
I can understand.
See, I've always
been more like May.
Charging into everything
headfirst is more my style.
I made fun of people
who said things like
"Let's all be friends
and do this together!"
"Those people are just cowards
who are afraid of getting hurt!"
I thought.
Sora... she's different from
those people I made fun of.
When I tried to make her
compete with May, she refused.
May thought she was
running away, but I could see
the fire in Sora's eyes, and
I knew that wasn't the case.
Some of the troupe members,
they've told me they don't
understand why Sora won't
stand up and compete with May.
They think she'd be more
humble if Sora beat her.
You know the people who are
telling you those things are
the people who don't have the
courage to fight themselves.
Those people make up about
80% of the population.
It's a lost cause.
I guess.
Remember the time Leon
pulled Sora onstage?
She gave a wonderful performance
even though May came after her.
There was something
thrilling about her.
I never felt the weakness of
someone who was running away.
But now it feels like
Sora's fighting against
herself somehow.
Maybe she's afraid.
I mean, maybe she fears that the
competition will never stop.
And she's constantly
battling that fear.
Look!
They're so beautiful!
That makes sense.
If her goal hadn't been
a stage without competition,
then it's possible she might
not have been able to come back
to the Kaleido Stage
when she did.
The force of the wave,
the force of the wind,
the force of the boat.
So many different forces
fighting each other.
This is more complicated than
the trapeze could ever be.
Try to sense the flow of each
of the different forces.
Don't think.
Feel it with your body.
Feel it with my body?
That's right.
If you can master that,
you'll always be able to land
your pose after you jump.
Yes sir!
Just make sure that
you hold your pose.
That's Sora for you.
She's on the right track now.
These trapeze are different
than at the Noir Circus.
That means you'll have
to use different timing
than you did then, got it?
Yes ma'am.
You can't let your body relax.
You keep slipping because you're
not picturing your next move.
You're the fairy of light.
Your role is to guide Odile
off the dark path of hatred
that she wandered down.
I have to try to show
the audience that Odile
is attempting to
overcome her own hatred.
Even though the only way she
can do that is with guidance
from a stronger power.
May...
You'll never be
a stronger power if you keep
performing this weakly!
We need to get this
basic stuff over with.
We have to move on to
our special training for
the Eternal Illusion.
"Eternal Illusion"?
So close.
Sorry about that.
I guess my timing was
just too fast on that one.
I can't believe you've
come this far on your own.
It's not perfect if I still
have to think about it.
I need to start
sensing it with my body.
Start changing the way you
channel your strength each time.
Do it like you would on stage.
Okay.
Thank you Sarah,
this is warming me up.
I figured I'd try cooking
some pork miso soup for you.
I hope you like it!
Is it yummy?
I'm sorry to say
I'm so exhausted
that I can't really taste it.
Oh, that's a shame!
I think this is
my best creation ever!
I even experimented
with adding fresh cream.
How is it, is it nice?
It's probably a good thing
I can't taste it.
Oh brilliant, Leon
would like a bowl too!
No.
The swans...
Mother Nature... an angel...
That's not it!
Eugh, why is this so hard!
What if I did
a goofy run like this?
The question is, do you
think the seal will like it?
Listen, the seal doesn't
have to like it, okay?
Oh, right!
This is agonizing.
I almost feel
like running away.
I think she's been
pushed to her limit.
The last time I felt like this
was when I was training for
the "Legendary Great Maneuver".
I was in so much pain.
The only reason
I could keep going
was because Layla led me on.
But Layla did it all on her own.
She didn't have
anyone to guide her.
She did it without
anyone's help.
She's not...
She did it!
So beautiful!
Layla.
She's an amazing performer.
With time,
it can only get better.
Huh?
This show is gonna
be really good!
Make sure to come and see it!
Do you think we could see
the lead, Sora Naegino?
Are you a fan of Sora's?
You could say that.
She's kinda busy lately.
She's been training at sea.
There she is!
Wha wha what's that
maneuver she's practicing?
It looks like it's part of
the "Angel's Maneuver".
Pretty!
Amazing!
She looks like an angel.
She is an angel!
Wow!
I just got the greatest idea!
How could I make it work?
The only way to beat Sora is to
do my very best playing Odile.
I'm gonna help make
this show the best ever.
I'll finally make my dream
come true on this stage.
Everyone's heart is
starting to become one.
Leon.
That's the stage
of a True Star.
Sophie.
It looks like I'll be able
to keep my promise.
I promise to keep practicing
right up until opening day!
I'm gonna make the true Kaleido
Star a reality, no matter what!
Hold on.
There's another candidate
of the role of Odette.
No way.
Tomorrow we'll hold an audition
for the role of Odette.
What?
An audition?
Could it be?
Sora's perfect for that.
Is it May?
Who is it?
Who is that?
It's Layla!
The competition is on, Sora.
And if you don't like it,
you'd better step down.
After all this time.
I never dreamed a day
like this would come.
I'm here because of
my admiration for you.
Your kindness and your cruelty.
The bond that we felt
that special day.
Do you remember?
I'll never forget.
Look at how far I've come.
Next time on Kaleido Star:
"A Most Amazing and
Inescapable Showdown".
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky.