Okay, everyone,
Kaleido Star is about to start.
So make sure that your
room is brightly lit
and that you're not
sitting too close to the TV.
Well, everyone, it's me, May.
I've been so depressed.
I failed last time. I failed.
And I've been moping
about it all by myself.
But I realized something
after Meryl talked to me.
I've just been
looking for excuses.
I've been blaming
things on somebody else.
My name is May Wong.
I'm an athlete who never
gives up, who never surrenders.
I won't let anybody
get in my way.
I'll work hard and win!
Sora, you're not the only one
trying to get to the
place where Layla is!
Congratulations!
Thanks, really. But I'm
wondering if this is okay?
Yes, it's okay.
Really?
Yeah, she's right.
Leon said you passed.
He's acknowledged you, Sora.
You think so?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, you're going
to the festival.
It's great. Good luck, Sora.
Thanks. I'll do my best.
Are you worrying
about May, Sora?
What?
Because I'm useless...
I know how you feel.
But for now, you should keep
your mind on the festival.
He's right, Sora.
Your goal is...
Okay, say it, everybody:
Victory!
Yeah, I know that.
Only one of us can
participate in the festival.
So if I want to go,
I can't think like this.
I have to beat May.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hello there.
Oh, it's you, Kalos.
What? Sora is here
with us, but...
Huh?
What?! Is that right?
There's a final test?
What?!
Did I hear you say ...
"final test"?
"The Two Amazing Demons."
I'll have them prepare for
the final test right away.
If she's going to
participate in the festival,
she has to take this test.
There's no way around it.
But if she has one misstep,
her career on the
stage may be over.
Are you prepared for that?
Sora can pull through this.
I believe that.
Just wait and see.
The final test.
If I can pass this, that
Phoenix Ticket will be mine.
No, I mustn't think about May.
This makes me so nervous.
I wonder what
kind of test it is.
No matter what it is,
she'll ace it.
Everyone is cheering you.
Thank you.
Hi, Layla...
Sora, I'll ask you one
more time. Be honest.
Do you seriously want to
participate in the Festival
no matter what happens to you?
Yes!
Well. That's fine, then.
Please do your best.
Yeah.
I have to pass this test.
No matter how difficult
the maneuver is, I have to.
There's no other alternative.
I'm ready. What should I do?
Go to the top.
Alright, what do
you want me to do?
Let's see. Why don't you
do a Layout Somersault?
What?
--What did he say?
--What's this about?
Hey, what's a Layout Somersault?
It's one of the most basic
maneuvers on the trapeze.
The performer spins once,
and grabs the catcher's hands.
That's all I have to do?
That's right.
Okay then.
Wait.
Remove the safety net.
WHAT?!
No! No way! You can't do that.
When you perform
in the festival,
there's no safety
net or lifeline.
Yeah that's true, but...
A basic maneuver like this
shouldn't require a safety net.
Do as I ask. I will give
you a chance to show off.
That's what he said to May.
Okay, I will give you a chance.
I will give you
the perfect chance
to show off in today's show.
Will you fail the final test
before you even take it?
Alright then. Remove the net.
Huh?
Remove it.
Yes.
A good attitude, Sora.
Now the moment of truth is here.
Show me how prepared you
are to be a real star.
Okay, let's go.
Next time, I'll jump.
Sora...
Hesitating is dangerous.
Jump like you mean it, Sora.
The timing's perfect.
I can do this!
I can't jump.
Sora!
Oh, no.
I thought "What would I do
if he didn't catch me"...
and then I couldn't jump.
P-Please let me try again.
When you do it for
real in the festival,
will you ask me to do it again?
Bu-But please!
Let me try one more--
Sora!
It's unseemly.
I'm sorry.
The way it is now,
this year's festival
could be no participation.
I know.
Leon walked away so easily.
I thought he would want to
participate in the festival
to erase the shame of
withdrawing three years ago.
But it seems I was wrong.
Why does he stay here?
It doesn't make any sense.
There was this rumor I heard.
He was looking for a partner
who could meet him at his level.
But he's had no luck.
All his partners so far
have left the stage.
Because he treats them all
like he treated May Wong.
But if that's the reason they
decided to leave the stage,
they never belonged there.
They're better off to quit
and get another career.
Leon knew that, yet
he still invited Sora.
Maybe he thought Sora
could be the partner
he had always been looking for.
And that with her,
he could win in the festival.
Even now, Sora is still trying
to follow in your footsteps.
In order for her to
surpass Layla Hamilton,
she has no other choice
but to win in the festival.
I think that's
the starting line.
So you still haven't
given up on your wish.
That's right.
You're the one who was first
attracted by Sora's potential.
You even pressured her
into appearing on the stage.
I'll do just about anything
if I can make money.
Kalos, if you were
actually capable of that,
Kaleido Stage would
never end up in a pinch.
I meant that as a compliment...
I wonder if Sora's all right.
She could have never done it.
Especially after she saw
what happened to May.
We should probably leave
her alone right now.
Okay.
I've endured so much. I even
endured that special training.
But I wasted everything today.
I disappointed myself;
I disappointed Layla.
Stupid! Stupid, Sora!
I just don't have confidence
in Leon as a partner.
What am I going to do?
You were able to perform
the legendary great
maneuver with Layla.
So why is it you can't do
a basic maneuver with Leon...
I could trust Layla.
But I can't trust Leon.
I just can't.
And that's why you fail.
A real star doesn't change her
light depending on who's there.
Are you saying ...
I can't be a real star?
I don't know that answer.
But by the way
you're acting now,
you're very far away from
ever becoming a real star.
It's far... far away?
Endlessly far away.
Sora!
Yeah?
May's missing!
She hasn't been in her room
since before last night.
No one knows where she is!
What? May's missing?
Get the ball, big sis!
Over here, over here!
Watch what you're doing.
Okay...
What's wrong with her?
Meryl...
I thought you would
be here. Found her.
Sora...
Why are you here?
Did you come to laugh at me?
What? No, no!
May, there's something I
want to talk to you about...
Stop it! What else could
you have to say to me now?!
Leon chose you over me.
You won fair and square.
So be proud of your victory.
And laugh at the pathetic loser!
May, I'm not here
to laugh at you...
Cut it out! You're making
me sick! Don't you get it?
I was a newcomer who picked
a fight with the top star.
And I grabbed the leading
role away from you.
I was feeling like hot stuff.
But I wasn't anything
but a tool to train you...
He injured my shoulder,
and I ran away.
Isn't it funny?
Go, laugh at me.
Laugh at me.
C'mon, laugh! There's no way
I want your sympathy!
You're wrong, May.
You see, I wasn't able
to pass Leon's final test.
It's true. I'm afraid of Leon.
When the moment came,
I couldn't let go of the swing.
I just couldn't.
What? Then, his partner
hasn't been decided yet?
No, not yet.
Oh...
You've been away
from the dormitory.
And you didn't
hear what happened.
So I knew I had to find
you and tell you this.
So you're not Leon's partner.
What can I do about that?
Uh, you could... Um...
Well, I don't know.
But I don't know what
I should do either.
What I want to say is...
Well, I'm not sure...
Where did you get that?
Your indecision
is so irritating.
--Sora!
--Um, yeah.
Is this why you came
all the way here?
So you could tell
May about your test?
Well... kinda...
--May!
--Yes, Meryl?
Really now. When did you
start giving up so easily?
I-I'm not giving up!
If you act like that,
you would be better off
had you listened to me
and kept on skating!
You can't do anything?
You don't know what
to do or where to go?
What malarkey. It seems to me
you just don't want to do it.
How can you say that?
It's not my fault. I was
abandoned by Leon!
You're wrong. Those are excuses.
You were injured because you
don't have enough skills.
To think you can't even handle
a little ad lib like that.
If you want to
blame it on something,
blame it on your lack of skills.
Don't act like
you're some victim.
The one who abandoned
you is you, May!
You did it to yourself!
The May I remember
was different.
When you were told "no,"
you wouldn't quit.
You worked so hard
that the person would
never be able to say
"no" to you again.
You never said you
couldn't do something.
You kept trying, no matter what!
Hey lady!
Lay off my sister!
Sister?
You, dumb kids!
Come and get us!
Na, na, na, na, na, na, na!
Yeah! Yeah!
We're number one!
There's a chance.
I may still have a chance.
May...
Thank you, Meryl.
Thank you for making me remember
how bad I am at giving up.
So, I'll challenge
Leon one more time.
It sounds like
you're motivated now.
Yeah, I am. I also have
to thank you too, Sora.
Thank you for taking your time
and coming all
the way down here.
I'm glad you let me know
you were disqualified.
I won't let this
chance get away.
I'll be his real
partner this time.
But ... aren't you
afraid of him?
In his dreams! Once he
sees my new maneuver,
I'm sure Leon will grab
hold of my hands this time.
And with that maneuver,
I'll get into the festival.
And I'll win.
And I'll make the world
acknowledge me
like they did Layla.
A new maneuver...
Yeah. And its name
is Demon Spiral!
Demon Spiral. What is that?
I don't know yet. I just
came up with the name.
As for the practice room,
I'll be using it.
Hey guys, I'm going
back to Kaleido Stage.
So do me a favor and
tell Mom and Dad, okay?
Yeah! Our big sis
is back to normal!
Really, she's so much trouble.
Well, Sora, what are
you going to do?
Are you going to just
stand there and watch?
Uh, no... But...
Did you say you can't
trust your partner?
Yeah.
You're just the same as May.
Blaming your lack of
skill on your partner.
That's just an excuse.
What?
Before you start
blaming your partner,
I suggest you look
closer to home.
Are you doing enough to
earn your partner's trust?
You're still not
fit to be my partner,
so I'll be reducing
your role even further
for tomorrow's show.
Instead of worrying
about something like that,
get the skills good
enough to satisfy me.
I agree it's important
for me to improve,
but I think Kids' Stage
is equally important.
You talk pretty, but aren't
you just running away?
Tell me, didn't you face Layla
Hamilton with all your might?
Did you hold anything back?
So then, why don't you
do the same thing now?
Because...
If you stay like this,
your path will be blocked.
You're the only one who can
cut your way through it.
Get it together!
Meryl, thank you.
I won't forget.
It's true. Back then, I faced
Layla like a daredevil.
But I don't have confidence
to act the same way with Leon.
How on Earth can I...
I don't like his attitude!
Let's dump him!
That's right!
Yeah, but if you ask who
else can play his role...
--There isn't anybody.
--Oh, that's true.
If we want to have an eye on
winning, I guess it's him...
Hey, why can't Sora
do it by herself?
Oh yeah!
Unfortunately, the rule is
she has to have a partner.
--Aw...
--Oh no.
That guy better watch out!
In three years, I'll do
all of his maneuvers easily.
Go, Rosetta! Go, go!
Excuse me, but I
asked everyone here
because I wanted
to encourage Sora.
So, if you're going to encourage
someone, please encourage her.
Uh... that's okay.
I'm thankful for the way
you all care about me.
But I'm going to have to
solve this problem on my own.
Really...
Sora, let me show you
this amazing martial art.
It can't be drawn
by human hands!
Oh no... Sarah...
--Here I go! Hiyaaah!
--Uh-huh. It's amazing!
She's right. No human
hand could draw that.
Sora, is this helpful?
Well... kinda...
Since nobody's here,
the air is cool.
That's right, the cool
space where I'm alone.
It's where I belong.
I only decided this after
I joined Kaleido Stage.
I was a newcomer.
And I wanted to bring
down a top star like Sora.
To do it even one second
or one minute faster,
I couldn't hang out
with the others.
I couldn't afford
to goof around.
If they don't like me,
they don't like me.
If they hate me, they hate me.
I'm going to win...
no matter what!
That move. He didn't have
both hands on the bar.
That's why he could make
that unexpected move.
If I can use it and
create a new maneuver...
One more time...
I will perfect this maneuver.
There's no other path
forward. Not for me.
To surpass Layla.
To become a real Kaleido Star.
That's why I want to participate
in the Circus Festival.
No matter what, I'll get there.
I'll get there! I'll get there!
But... I still don't
know what I should do.
And May has already
found something
and started running toward it.
Taurus escaped the darkness.
But it still
engulfs Sagittarius.
Sora, if you expend
effort without focus,
you'll just spin in place.
Then, tell me what
I'm supposed to do.
There you are. Sora!
Oh, Rosetta. Good morning.
No time for small talk.
C'mon, let's hurry.
What?
May's going to
challenge Leon again.
May's... doing what?
Who knew you would be the one
to ask me for another challenge.
I was intrigued
by what you said.
This new maneuver is
supposed to satisfy me?
Of course, it will, Leon.
You're the only one can
catch my Demon Spiral.
If you screw up even slightly,
I'll fall for sure.
If you're the God of Death,
then I will be a devil.
The Demon Spiral is a challenge
from a devil to
the God of Death.
I expect you to accept.
Here I go.
Whoa!
That's right. This is
the match with my fate!
Now...
Demon! Spiral!
A-Amazing!
When I was at Kaleido Stage,
I don't remember looking at
the faces of the audience much.
And so, May created the
Demon Spiral. It was amazing!
I can't back down now.
Besides, being bad at giving
up is something I've patented!
Well, if it's with him...
All right! I'll show them
what I can do when I'm serious!
I'll show them! I'll show them!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Amazing Angelic Counterattack."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...