It is now time to watch Kaleido
Star, so keep your room bright,
sit far enough away from
the TV, and wait for
the hour of your fate.
Well, well, well.
As the Fool said,
'The time is now.'
Finally, Layla and I
are going to attempt
the Legendary Great Maneuver!
It's been a really rough road,
and I've thought
about quitting a lot.
But this show is going to make
all my hard work worthwhile.
The next tears I cry will be
tears of joy! Tears of joy!
Why fear it when
it won't happen?
We'll perform the
maneuver perfectly.
The time is now.
You both were
chosen by the stage,
and you have persevered
through many hardships.
You have finally earned
the right to learn about
the Legendary Great Maneuver.
You must only attempt
this maneuver if you have
unshakable confidence. Now
I will tell you all I know.
'An Amazing Comeback.'
What's going on?
The spirit of the stage must
be here. Instructing them.
Huh?
I think you're right.
Anyone wishing to attempt
the Legendary Great Maneuver
must have great confidence.
Once they tell the spirit
they have no fear of failure,
no fear of death, he
begins to instruct them.
Oh. But what would happen
if they said they were
afraid of dying?
Then the spirit of the
stage would've disappeared
and we'd have been
forced to cancel.
Unless they decided
to perform anyway...
So that's the
Legendary Great Maneuver?
Amazing.
It's even better
than I imagined.
I think the best thing would be
for you to rest your shoulder
and for me to rehearse more.
That way, both of us
will be ready for tomorrow!
That sounds perfect. Mia?
Yes?
I'd like to talk to you about
the set we'll be on tomorrow.
Could you pass my suggestions
along to the director?
Sure.
Everything is in motion.
Your wait is almost over:
tomorrow Sora Naegino
and Layla Hamilton will attempt
the Legendary Great Maneuver!
Good! Keep that height
and rhythm, people!
And after that, Layla
says they'll need to switch
to the trampoline.
All of you will wait at
this gate until it's time
for your entrance.
Hey, Anna!
Hey! You guys all came!
Of course we did.
There's no way we were
gonna just sit at home.
So what's the deal with this
Legendary Great Maneuver, huh?
I don't know.
I've just rebuilt what
Arlon had me build years ago.
One, two, jump!
Yeah!
Higher, folks you've really
got to get up there!
Yay, that was incredible!
Hi, Marion, Jonathan!
Come see!
Everybody has come back!
What?
Everyone from
Freedom Rights is here.
Even the people who quit
Kaleido Stage came back
just to see this, Sora!
Really?
Kaleido Stage is just
the way it used to be!
We did it!
I haven't seen you in a while.
The last time was at that
festival in Vancouver. Right?
That's right.
I'm going to Asia
on business tomorrow
so I don't have much time here.
Why don't you just
tell me what you want.
You need to see
Layla's show tomorrow.
It's extremely important.
I figured you'd say
something like that.
You see, I've already
heard Kaleido Stage
is going up for sale.
Well, you couldn't be more
wrong if you think I'm the man
who'll help you keep it
I got out of that venture
and I've never been happier.
You and I are two of a kind,
do you know that?
Isn't it funny? I tried to
create the Kaleido Stage
I thought my Father
would've wanted.
But it turns out, all the things
I thought were important weren't
his priorities at all.
I wasn't trying to understand.
Just like you don't ever try
to understand how
your daughter feels.
I don't try to
understand? Ridiculous.
I'm a fool. I've been fixating
on a wrong that never existed.
And now I know that my
Father would've hated
what I've been doing.
And you're a fool for making
your daughter choose between
her love for you and her
love for Kaleido Stage.
Make no mistake, she can
live without your help.
She can do more than
that she can fly.
Honestly, I've never seen anyone
who was as good as Layla.
But it doesn't matter
what I think of her,
because the only one
she wants to please is you.
But you're too busy with
your money to notice that.
You've been blind, Hamilton.
Did you at least enjoy
what I did out there?
So tomorrow I'm
reserving you a seat.
Hi, Mom. It's me.
That's right, the show's
going to be tomorrow night.
I'm really sorry about
the short notice on this...
Oh, really? How's Yume? Ohhh.
No, don't worry about that.
I've already
reserved your seats.
So, how's the pain
in your shoulder?
Better. I should be able to
perform tomorrow after all.
It's funny...
I'm usually really nervous
before opening a new production.
But I haven't felt
this calm in years.
I can't wait to step
on that stage tomorrow.
As your doctor, I want
to remind you again that
performing with that shoulder
is a terrible idea.
But I know you're going
to do it anyway so I promise
I'll do everything
I can to get you through
that show tomorrow night.
Yeah that's great. Thanks Kate.
Sora, are you in here?
No way! She can do all
that with just one arm?!
Hey, Rosetta!
Oh wow. This is gonna be great!
Sora.
We're all ready
for the show, too.
Layla...
And then after they finish
with that routine, the rest of
the cast is going to
clear off of the stage.
Then it's time for you to do the
maneuver. This'll be your set.
Now I know how you must've felt
when my father went on stage
for the last time.
The performers chosen by
the spirit have to attempt
the Legendary Great Maneuver.
Nothing can keep them from it.
No.
I wanted to make Kaleido Stage
a place where no performer
was injured or
killed ever again.
I never meant
to destroy this place.
You haven't lost
Kaleido Stage yet.
Things could still
look up for you.
You've actually done
a pretty good job.
You know, before your father
died I considered making him
our business manager.
Really? I guess he probably
would've had the sense
to let you keep Kaleido Stage.
No one can nurture talent like
you. Sora's a testament to that.
I can't take credit for her.
She dashed into this
thing all by herself.
So. Tomorrow's the day...
Yep. This time tomorrow
night we'll be on stage.
The Legendary Great Maneuver...
We're gonna show
that audience something
they've never seen before.
Now, the swing is longer than
the one we used in practice,
so make sure to
watch your timing.
Right.
You and I are gonna
go out on that stage
and do the
impossible this evening.
Yes. But, Layla do you mind
if I ask you something?
Go ahead.
What would you have done
if the Fool had decided we
weren't ready to learn about
the maneuver yesterday.
If he hadn't thought
we were qualified?
I never doubted that
he would tell us.
What? You mean never,
not even once?
No. Honestly, it never
crossed my mind that
he wouldn't find us qualified.
But that's usually how
I feel when I decide
I'm going to do something.
What about you?
What, me? Well, I guess
I felt the same as you did.
It it sounds like they're
both laughing. Hey, Sora?
Yes?
You have some visitors.
I'll be right there.
Hello, Sora.
You made it! I'm so glad!
Yume... Have you
been a good girl?
Thank you for inviting us.
No, I'm the one who
should be thanking you guys
for coming all this way.
We're just so glad that you
asked us to be here for you.
Just a few months ago you never
would have asked, because you
thought traveling would be too
much trouble for us, remember?
Yeah. I guess you're right.
You wanted to fly in and
out of Cape Mary on the day
of your audition
to save us a hotel bill.
I'd forgotten about that.
I was so worried about her.
Yeah. It wasn't
the greatest idea...
Sora, you seem to be
in good spirits today.
Yes, I think you
seem very confident.
I am. That's why I wanted the
both of you to be here so badly.
Oh, and you too, Yume.
We're not your only
family who'll be here.
After all,
you have four parents.
And every one of us
will be cheering you on.
You're extremely pushy,
you know that?
Say what you want about me,
but please keep an open mind.
Just watch the show
tonight and tell me if you
still wanna sell Kaleido Stage.
Look, kid, it's already sold.
Mr. Kenneth?
Then maybe I should consider
buying it back again.
By yourself? That's ridiculous.
You'd take a bath on it.
A bit of advice: people who
don't take chances won't reap
the greatest rewards
of this life, chump.
Just keep it nice
and still, Sora.
Right.
Once we do the
Legendary Great Maneuver,
I think the audiences will
start coming back here.
I think so too.
And when they come back
we'll have to have a new
production for them.
Something both kids
and adults can enjoy,
just like the old days.
Oh, how is everybody?
Good, I hope.
They're all fine.
That's what I like to hear.
The final card is The Fool,
foretelling almost
unlimited possibilities.
The door to great things will
only be opened for those
foolish enough not to be afraid.
It doesn't look like
they're wearing lifelines.
That means that if they drop...
That would be awful.
This performance with Layla
is gonna be the best
Kaleido Stage ever.
Sora...
I don't know.
This is making me nervous...
They're really high up there,
but it still feels like I could
touch them. It feels
just like magic.
Are you ready, Sora?
Yes.
Just focus on
what Layla's doing.
Let's do this Sora.
Jump towards Layla. Now!
Amazing.
They did it!
They're flying!
They really are!
It's like they both grew
wings. It's incredible!
H-How is something
like that possible?!
I always knew those girls
would pull this off.
As long as I can
stay up here with Layla
I won't ever be afraid.
I'm so happy I feel like crying.
I don't ever want
this moment to end.
I want to keep performing
like this forever!
An absolute faith in life,
one so complete
that it knows no fear.
That is the
Legendary Great Maneuver.
I see now. The
Legendary Great Maneuver
displays such faith in life,
it keeps death at bay.
That's why we thought
it was impossible.
But to find faith
as great as theirs...
Arlon I think you must
have glimpsed it:
an act so powerful it gives
all who see it new strength...
Amazing. And I thought
I had the power to stand
in the way of this...
Sora, it's time to go back.
Right.
It looks like the wind is
pushing the swings further out.
We'll have to push harder.
I'm ready.
One. Two. Three!
It it's over now.
Quick, dim the lights on Layla.
Now? But I--
Do it. Right now.
Sure.
Layla's hurt.
That was great!
Sora, you're my hero!
Perfect! I've never
seen anything like it!
Sora, you did it.
How strange, it still
feels like I'm flying.
Layla.
Father?
That was a wonderful show.
You were watching?
Yes. And now I understand
what Yuri meant.
Yuri?
You really can fly and you
don't need my help to do it.
You've become a remarkably
strong young woman, Layla.
Father, thank you.
Did you hurt your
shoulder up there?
Yes.
Is it bad?
I think it is. There's no way
I'll ever be able to perform
at Kaleido Stage again.
What?
Do you really mean that?
Yes, I do.
It can't it can't be...
Kate told me this would probably
happen. But I had to do this.
We achieved the impossible
and got the best applause.
But if this has to be my last
show ever, I couldn't have
wished for a better performance
or a better partner.
But you...
it can't... it can't be
Sora!
Sora.
Sora, you have to be strong.
But I can't I can't!
When I decided to attempt
the Legendary Great Maneuver
with you, I knew
there would be a price.
But I was willing
to try this with you,
no matter what
the risks might be.
Sora. Today before the show
you told me you never doubted
you'd be able
to do the maneuver.
I need you to have
that kind of faith now.
You need to stand up, Sora.
Sora from now on
I want you to be my dream.
I'm putting all
my faith in you, Sora.
You want me to be
your dream, Layla?
I do. Because I know you
have what it takes to be
a true Kaleido Star.
A true Kaleido Star...
Sora!
Sora? Come on, hurry!
Hey, Sora!
Coming!
For Layla, I'm going to
become a true Kaleido Star,
no matter what it takes.
I will! I will!
Looks like I've got
a long way to go...
Hi, everybody! I bet you all
want to know what it was like
to do the Legendary
Great Maneuver.
Well, it was really hard.
I cried a lot and we
trained all the time.
But it was a great feeling
when we finally did it.
And now that Layla
can't perform anymore,
I'm gonna work hard to
make her dream come true.
I'm going to become a Kaleido
Star for her, no matter what.
I'll do it! I'll do it!
Don't miss the next
episode of Kaleido Star,
'The Amazing Prologue
to Stardom (Part 1)'
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...