Hey, everyone,
Kaleido Star's about to start.
So make sure that your
room is brightly lit
and that you're not
sitting too close to the TV.
Well, well, well.
Have you ever had times
when you didn't know
what you wanted to do?
Or where you wanted to go?
Well, that's exactly the
way I'm feeling right now.
I worked hard, trying to
get into Kaleido Stage.
Then I worked hard so I would
be acknowledged by everyone.
And then I worked hard
trying to catch up with Layla.
But I wonder what I'm
working hard for now?
No! Not good. Not good.
I can't become a star feeling
all wishy-washy like this.
I can't! I can't! I can't!
That's right. This is
a match with my fate!
Now!
Demon! Spiral!
Her movement is too irregular;
I can't even follow it.
Amazing. But can he grab her?
Oh, no! She's not high enough!
A devil's maneuver?
That certainly
might be appropriate
for a partner of mine.
You mean...
It's been decided.
"Amazing Angelic Counterattack."
Sora's been through a lot,
but this must be a shock.
Yeah, I don't even know
what to say to her.
Let's leave her alone for now.
Sora...
Demon Spiral...
May had a shoulder injury,
but she didn't
let that stop her.
She used it to invent
a new maneuver.
And she got the Phoenix Ticket.
While I...
Sora...
Layla...
You know, I was stunned, too.
I didn't think May
would go that far.
I was actually quite
impressed that she
took advantage of her injuries
to invent a new maneuver.
I'm sorry, Layla.
Three years ago,
before Yuri and I
participated in the Circus
Festival, we got a message...
to meet with Kalos.
Good. You're here.
Listen carefully, both of you.
If you can't win,
don't come back.
What?!
If you don't win in
the Circus Festival,
there's no place for
you at Kaleido Stage.
Did Kalos really say that?
Yes, he did.
That's why I had no other
choice. I had to win.
But, with all that pressure,
you still won the match
with your own fate.
You're really amazing.
What will you do now?
I guess I'll improve my skills.
That way I'll keep up with May.
Sora, really.
I can't believe this.
Do you think you lost to May
because you didn't
have enough skills?
Huh?
Look, if you didn't
have the skills,
I would never have recommended
you in the first place.
No, it's something else.
You lost the festival because
it only meant so much to you.
What? No, you're wrong!
To me, it was something
I needed to enter and to win
no matter what it took.
To me, it was worth
that much effort.
To you, however, it
wasn't worth that much.
Sora, I'll ask you one
more time. Be honest.
Do you seriously want to
participate in the Festival
no matter what happens to you?
Yes!
Once you make up your mind
to get something done,
you never give it up.
That's something I know
better than anyone else.
But here you are right now,
and you've given up
on everything.
To me, that's proof you weren't
serious about it at all.
I think I told you
after the Salome show.
I can't feel enough of a
competitive edge from you
right now to be afraid of you.
You've lost track
of what's important.
I wanted you to
enter the festival.
Wait, Layla!
I can't believe
what I did...
I...
I disappointed Layla.
I let her down.
Sora, Sora! Untape me!
I want to do something.
I have to do something!
What can I do?
What? Tell me, Fool.
I don't know the answer to that.
Well, you're no help.
And I thought you were
supposed to be on my side.
Can't you give me some clever
advice or something like that?
I'm a spirit of the stage.
So I am neither friend nor foe.
One more chance. I want
to have one more chance.
Oww! I can't believe
this is happening to me!
I am so pathetic!
The only thing I can
tell you is this.
The deadline for Circus Festival
entries hasn't passed yet.
The Sagittarius is still not
able to get out of the darkness.
But nearby, I can see
another arrow, a bright arrow.
It points as if it's
showing her the way out.
One more arrow?
Phoenix Tickets are
the "seed" right.
They're given to the
two people who won.
Two... two!
Hey! There's one more ticket!
Hmm...
Ticket! Ticket! Ticket!
--There's one more ticket!
--I can't... I can't breathe.
I just wet myself.
You know, Yuri is studying
in Paris right now.
The Circus Festival
is held in Paris, too.
So it's perfect!
Take me to Paris, quick!
Paris?
Wait, Yuri hasn't
even registered!
And we don't know
that he wants to.
And you can't take
a taxi to Paris.
Impossible or not,
there's nothing to do but ask!
I realized I can't keep
moping about how I lost to May.
I just have to
acknowledge my defeat
and do what I can do now.
I'll be away from
Kids' Stage for a while,
but everything should be okay.
I talked to Marion,
and she's fine with it.
Do you think Sora's
back to normal?
If it's true, there's nothing
we can do to stop her now.
Sora!
Rosetta!
Here's a guide book to Paris.
I used it when I was there.
It has some French phrases,
too, although it's not much.
Thank you. It'll help.
Also, here's a winter coat.
It gets cold
over there you know.
Thank you, Rosetta.
Bye!
Go, Sora!
She's lucky.
Someday I'll go to Paris...
and see Mr. Charlie the clown.
So, you're rarin' to go, too?
Well, if you put it like
that, I'm Parin' to go!
Je... Je... Je t'aime.
Why that's...
The God of Death's come back!
Wait here. I'll check us in.
Wow.
Leon. It's been a long time.
So, you remember me?
I'm touched.
And you. Are you
his new partner?
Yes. I'm Leon's partner.
I'm May Wong.
Poor thing.
Once the Circus Festival is
over, you'll be discarded, too.
Hey, Lady! Who do
you think you are?!
Hey, you better not put us on
the same floor as Leon Oswald!
Being near him makes
my performers nervous.
If you can't do this,
I'll change hotels!
Yes, of course, sir.
Oh. This is a message for
Ken Robbins of Kaleido Stage.
That is you, no?
What? For me?
"I'll give you a
chance to show off."
So, did you hear it, too?
The whisper of the God of Death?
I will give you a chance.
I will give you
the perfect chance
to show off in today's show.
"The whisper of
the God of Death"?
How do you know that?
Were you his partner too?
Partner? Nobody can
be Leon's partner.
Nobody but her.
But "her"?
Sora's here?
Uh, let's see...
This is where I am.
The drama school
where Yuri is...
I can't read French!
Where? Where? Where?!
Where are you, Yuri!
I see. I'll try to look
for her too. Goodbye.
Alright Sora,
where could you be?
Er, uh... Me-Merci.
Now I'm broke.
I spent the last of
my money on that cab.
But at least... Yuri's here.
Non.
What? Not here?
Mais, c'est bien ici
le Conservatoire...
Sorry...
--What am I gonna do?
--If you're looking for Yuri...
He wasn't in the class today.
What? So, he's here
at the school?
Yeah.
Liar!
Uh. Excuse me, but do you know
where I can find Yuri now?
He, uh, marches to his own beat.
Or you could say he's kind
of difficult to approach.
Hey, I don't know.
Well, where does he live?
No idea. Sorry. Bye.
It's a dead end. What now?
The Circus Festival!
I'm sure... I'm sure
Yuri will come here, too.
I'm sure! I'm sure!
Oh... So, this is the hall.
Wow, they're performing!
Huh?
Merci, merci.
Oh, I know! If I make
some money here,
I can keep looking for Yuri,
and I can eat something!
I'm not at a dead end yet.
Not yet! Not yet!
Hey, they're getting fired up.
Oh. Hi, Mute and Alice.
She's quite a performer,
isn't she?
She's amazing. But I've
never seen her before.
She's pretty good. Who is she?
Ta-da!
Oh, no...
Superb!
Brava!
Oh? Merci! Merci! Merci! Wow!
Now I can buy
something to eat. Huh?
Hey, are you all right?
Did you hurt yourself?
Oh. I can understand him.
What luck.
What?! What was that? Hey!
Really. I thought you
hurt yourself back there.
I was worried.
Who would have ever thought
she was just hungry?
Sorry. I'm starving.
I haven't eaten anything
since I got to Paris.
You were famished and you
still performed like that?
How impressive.
Well, I had to do it.
I want to enter
the Circus Festival.
What? You're going to
participate in the festival?
I want to! What about you,
Alice and Mute?
We do. We're like you.
We want to win the festival
and get the world's attention.
But it's not only for ourselves.
If we win, we'll organize
a performance team
with these guys right here.
And then travel around the
world. That's our dream.
And the weight of
everyone's dream...
rests heavily on
Mute's shoulders.
I guess.
Wow! What a great dream!
Sora, didn't you also come here
to make your dream come true?
Well, then... Don't give up.
Somewhere out there, an angel
always keeps an eye on us.
An angel... who keeps
an eye on us...
Sora!
Yeah?! Huh?
Hello Sora.
Yuri!
Yuri? I think
that's Yuri Killian.
Does she know Yuri Killian,
the winner of the last festival?
I don't believe this.
Who is she?
Yuri!
Finally. I found you.
But I was sure you
would come here.
I just knew it!
Who ever thought I would
see you somewhere like this.
It's been a long time.
Yeah. It has a
different atmosphere
from America or Japan.
It's relaxing, isn't it?
Yeah.
It looks like you've completely
adjusted to life in Paris.
You think so?
Yeah.
Well... To tell you the truth,
I didn't come to Paris for fun.
I came to ask you for a favor.
A favor? What kind?
The big kind. Did you receive
Phoenix Tickets this year?
Yes. What about them?
Let's use them.
Yuri, I want to participate in
the Circus Festival with you.
Wow, that is a big favor, Sora.
Please, Yuri! Help me!
You're my last hope.
You're the only one
that can help.
Sora, it wasn't an accident
I was walking by
the festival today.
I went over there looking for
you, because Layla asked me to.
What? Layla asked you?
And I heard the gist of what
happened at Kaleido Stage.
You really are determined to
follow your dream, aren't you?
Does this mean...
But I think it's too
tough for you to handle.
Huh? Why do you say that?
Sora, you don't know
the nature of this festival.
It's a place where you
make your dream come true.
But at the same time,
it's a place where you
destroy the dreams of others.
That's the kind of place
the Circus Festival is.
I already know that, Yuri.
I also know victory means
beating everyone else
and destroying their dreams
to make mine come true.
But there's no other choice.
If I want to be a real Kaleido
Star, I have to win here.
Fair play, friendship, and
consideration don't exist.
Let down your guard,
and you'll get jumped.
It's that kind of world.
Still interested?
Yeah, I can handle it.
Okay. Then let me
give you an example.
Your friend Ken.
Just before you perform,
you get a call
saying he's collapsed.
He's in the hospital and he
says he really wants to see you.
He's very sick.
What do you do, Sora?
Well, I'd have to go...
Are you sure about that?
The call might be a lie
made up by another performer.
Oh, yeah. I hadn't
thought of that.
Sorry. I think I was being
a little mean with
those questions.
All right then.
Yuri...
Let's participate
in the festival.
I'll make an application
for our entry tomorrow.
Thank you, thank you!
So this is where you live?
Wow... Did you paint
all of these, Yuri?
Yep. What with spending all
my time here and at school,
I started wanting some company.
So I picked up a brush,
and got into it.
Everyone is smiling.
When I was at Kaleido Stage,
I don't remember
looking at the faces
of the audience much.
But when I started painting...
I realized just how wonderful
smiling faces could be.
Is this the picture
you're painting now?
Yes. When I tried to get at
the essence of the smile,
it became an angel.
Angel...
It's May.
I'd like to start training
soon, if that's okay.
All right.
So, this is it.
Leon Oswald, you say?
Yeah, that's right.
Leon and May are
doing a maneuver
called the Demon Spiral.
I suppose we'll need
something on the same level.
Shall we try an
Angel's Maneuver?
An Angel's... Maneuver?
That's right. To compete
with their Demon Maneuver.
Yes.
Sora?!
Hey, we'd liked to help.
Alice and Mute!
You don't have much time
to practice for the show.
And we can also learn
something from watching
the winner of the
previous festival.
So helping you helps us.
Well, Sora?
Since they're
willing to help us,
I think we should
accept their offer.
We accept.
Oh, thank you.
That's great!
Wow. Even among those
who enter to the festival,
there are nice people
like Mute and Alice.
Good! Now, go up higher!
No. That's not good at all.
Okay!
Like you're flying
upwards on your own power!
Yeah!
I won't lose to May!
I'll win this time!
I'll rise to meet
Layla's expectations.
Demon Spiral!
This is the fastest you can go?
--No! I can do faster!
--Then go as fast as you can!
Okay!
That's right. Do it more slowly.
Like an angel's wings...
Right!
I see. The winning
candidate's maneuver...
I'm going to win...
no matter what!
And the one to win...
will be me!
Perhaps a match with you
is my unavoidable destiny.
And so, it's showtime!
What? Yuri and Leon
know each other?
Wait! What happened
between the two of them?
How should I know?
What I saw during the battle
was betrayal and despair.
Something I believed
in is shattering!
Shattering! Shattering!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Cruel Amazing Festival."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...