Hey everyone,
Kaleido Star's about to start,
so make sure that your
room is brightly lit,
and that you're not
sitting too close to the TV.
Well, well, well,
have your friends ever asked
you to do something for them?
When you see someone you
care about having a hard time,
you just can't
turn away, can you?
I know that I was only able to
get this far at Kaleido Stage
because lots of
people helped me out.
Now it's my turn to help.
Oh, Rosetta, please
don't look so sad.
It'll be all right.
Don't worry. Let me handle this!
It's my turn to help
you this time, okay?
Okay? Okay?
"The Amazing Newcomer."
I hate it!
I want you to
teach it right now!
You mustn't be impatient.
I simply can't--
I can't stand it
for another second!
Don't be so irritated, May.
Why don't you give this a try?
Since you're from China,
I bet you probably
know all about this,
the Cat's Paw style
of martials arts.
I don't know any
phony martial arts!
Phony?
I can't ignore
what you just said!
--Never mind that.
--Never mind that?!
Hold on!
If what you said is true,
what about my week-long
correspondence course?
How should I know?
Oh, I'm so irresponsible.
I don't have anything
to do with that!
I can not believe this.
I'm gobsmacked.
Anyway, do something
about this right away!
Now, now, now, both of you.
I refuse to live in the
room underneath Sora's.
Since I'm going to be
a big star one day,
it's not right that I should
have to live under her room.
So please, change my
dorm room right now.
--She's unbelievable.
--Now! Now! Now!
I'm the one who's supposed
to unite Kaleido Stage,
now that Layla
isn't here anymore.
But Layla was really
different from you.
Mia's right, you're not gonna
get anywhere by overdoing it.
I got it!
I'll throw a party!
You'll throw a party?
Yeah, a welcoming party!
We can invite
Mr. Oswald and May,
and if they have fun, I'm sure
they'll be friendlier.
But what if they don't have fun?
Oh no.
No, it'll be all right.
Yeah! I'm gonna go talk to Sarah
about it in a little while.
How could she come up with
hosting a welcoming party
after what May just
said to her down there?
If I were gonna be a gag
character, I'd be Sora.
Do you really wanna
be a gag character?
Of course.
Of course I'll need
a cake, and then--
Was there a break-in?
It sounds like
someone's in the shower.
But would a burglar use the
shower in the middle of a job?
Fool!
It all happened
so quickly, Sora.
I missed my chance.
Ah, she's coming.
I'm not sure what's
going on here,
but I'm getting you
out of the way.
Leave me alone, I want to see.
Oh my! Rosetta!
Oh, Sora! Welcome back.
But I-I live here.
I borrowed your shirt.
What are you doing
out here in the dark?
Oh, I... nothing.
I guess I should ask you
what you're doing in my room.
You've got to help me!
So your agent is after you?
That's right... because
I told her that I wanted
to come back to Kaleido Stage
and perform with you again.
What?
It's true.
But my agent is such a blockhead
that she refused to listen
to what I had to say.
You came here to
join Kaleido Stage?
Yes. I had to.
After I saw you and Layla do
the legendary great maneuver,
I was so moved.
And I thought,
"I wanna hear that kind of
amazing applause for me,
one day, too." I need it, Sora.
And that's why...
it's impossible for me to
go back to my agent ever again.
Oh please, Sora,
will you please help me?
Rosetta, I'll do anything
I can to help you out,
since you've helped me
so much in the past, but...
If my agent finds me,
she's going to punish me.
What? She's gonna
punish you how?
Uh, that is...
You mean, like she'll give
you ten lashes or something?
Not ten, she'd
give me a thousand!
A thousand!
Anyway, you're the only person
I can depend on right now.
Hmm.
I'm so glad.
And I'll help you out by
cleaning and doing laundry,
so if you need me to do
anything, just ask me okay?
Okay.
Right's clear,
left's clear, the front...
So, uh, you were able to
switch rooms after all!
Once I have my welcome party,
we're all gonna get along.
We are! We are!
When she's asleep, she looks
like a normal little girl,
not some kind of
diabolo prodigy.
I have to make sure
I keep her safe.
Stars have appeared that
will affect Sora's sign.
There are so many
bright new players,
they almost outshine her
hopes for the future.
She has difficult times ahead.
But then again, the path
to being a Kaleido Star
has always been an arduous one.
How'd I get down here?
Oh, May!
Get in the elevator!
Shut, shut, shut!
Sora, you're amazing!
You're eating enough for two!
I just... woke up really
hungry this morning.
Well I'm gonna triple
Sora's portions.
Well, I just think I'll
eat in my room today.
That's probably a good idea.
--Bye.
Oh yeah, you guys,
I'm having a welcoming party
in my room tonight,
so please come.
--Did she say "welcoming party"?
--Hey, I want you to come, too.
I can't wait!
Right, hope to see you there!
Kaleido Star.
Amazing! Amazing!
All right.
Welcome back, Sora.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
now let's eat.
Oh, I tried to do some dishes.
I-I see.
I hope you didn't hurt yourself.
Then I tried to clean
the place up a bit.
Oh, thanks.
And then I tried to
replace a light bulb.
--I can see that.
--I'm really sorry.
Hey, Sora.
Please help me.
I'm trapped in here.
I wasn't paying attention,
and I got sucked in.
It's, uh, kind of embarrassing,
so uh, you'll help
me out, right?
I think it's time for
breakfast, don't you?
Hey, Sora, how did it feel to do
the legendary great maneuver?
--How did it feel?
--Yeah...
Weren't you kinda scared?
No, not at all.
I mean, during practice
I worried a lot.
And I got really nervous, but...
I was okay, 'cause
I was with Layla.
Can I tell you something?
I want to be a trapeze
artist, just like you.
What?
Are you serious, Rosetta?
Mhmm.
Hold on, I don't think we can
make those changes right now.
If you increase my stage time,
the quality of this
production will go up.
Mr. Oswald,
Sora is your partner.
Why are you doing this?
I'm not asking to
eliminate her completely.
But she'd only be on
stage five minutes.
And I'm telling
you that right now,
that's all the time she's worth.
If she doesn't like it, she
doesn't have to be in the show.
Leon's suggestion is reasonable.
Do what he says.
Right.
In exchange for that,
will you promise
never to walk out
in the middle of a show again?
I cannot guarantee you that.
But...
Well, I'm going.
Right, good luck today.
And, uh, promise not to take
any more baths or showers
while I'm gone, okay?
Uh, I promise.
Now that was uncalled for.
Hi, Kaleido Stage.
No way!
Sorry, Sora, we didn't
have any other options.
Most of the ensemble routines
have been shortened as well.
This is turning into
Leon's one-man show.
These are Mr. Oswald's
instructions?
Yes.
I understand how
you feel about this,
but right now Kaleido Stage
really needs a star
like Leon Oswald, so...
Hey, it's alright.
Let's stop moping and do our
best to make the show exciting!
Yeah!
You're right!
Everyone here is gonna do their
best out on that stage today.
That's great, but there's only
one thing I ask of you people.
Do not get in my way.
That is my one request.
You said Rosetta?
Yes.
I haven't heard anything
about her coming here.
I figured as much.
Well, if you do hear
something, give me a call.
I certainly will.
By the way, Sora's performances
don't seem very lively lately.
So you've noticed it, too?
After all, I'm Sora's
first and biggest fan.
I know that losing Layla must
have been really hard for her.
I hope this new guy
you've got in the company
turns out to be a good
partner for Sora.
Ahh!
Hmm?
By any chance,
are you able to see me?
I am called the Fool.
I'm the spirit of the stage.
The chosen few who can see me
are destined to become
truly great performers.
As I have already found
those who could perform
the legendary great maneuver,
my new task is to find someone
who will be a real star--
Oh, I can't wait
to try the trapeze!
So she can't see me after all.
We only have one matinee
performance today,
so why don't you and I go
see the boss after that?
I wonder if I could go see a
little bit of Sora's show today.
Huh, the practice rooms...
I wonder what people
are practicing.
Absolutely wonderful! You're
very impressive, May Wong.
Of course I am!
Oh, and so confident!
Instructor, please tell
me you'll let me appear
in a real performance
sometime soon?
What?
To be frank with you,
I'm much more talented
than Sora Naegino ever was.
I think you should hurry up
and kick her off the stage
and make me your
new leading lady.
I think everyone should
just admit the truth.
I, for one, feel sorry
for Leon Oswald,
having that amateur
as a partner.
Kaleido Stage doesn't need
a loser like Sora Naegino.
Don't you agree?
Why?
What gives you the right to
talk about Sora like that?
Who are-
You have no idea
what she's capable of.
Oh, I know what
her abilities are.
But they're no match for
the kind of talent I have.
My friend Sora's amazing,
but I wouldn't expect someone
like you to know that.
Huh? Aren't you that Rosetta?
--Rosetta? The diabolo girl?
--Uh, no!
I didn't recognize you.
You may be a genius
at diabolo, Rosetta,
but this is a
Kaleido Stage matter,
and it's not your concern!
Rosetta?
Oh, good, it is you.
Hey, your agent's
looking for you.
Give her a call and let
her know where you are.
You're still not fit
to be my partner.
So I'll be reducing
your role even further
for tomorrow's show.
Right.
This isn't how Kaleido Stage
is supposed to be.
I wonder if we can continue
to create productions
with someone like this.
Leon looked so great.
I'm coming back tomorrow.
I just saw her run into
Kaleido Stage, over.
Thank you.
Hmm?
I'm sorry Rosetta
has imposed on you.
Not at all.
But I wonder why she decided to
come out here to Kaleido Stage.
Me too.
Rosetta! Rosetta!
Hey, Rosetta!
Rosetta?
That's right, Sora,
she just ran through here.
This way!
Rosetta!
The agent who'll give
her a thousand lashes!
Where'd she go?
She ran this way.
Rosetta!
Rosetta, get down here!
I won't, now go!
Rosetta, enough!
Wait a minute!
Listen to what
Rosetta has to say.
She wants to become a
member of Kaleido Stage.
She what?
I'm ending the contract
with my agent.
You can pay me a
newcomer's salary,
so Kalos, what do you say?
Yeah, that sounds great.
Well, I'm not going to
let you have your way.
We should take her
wishes into cons-
You won't be able to do
this on your own, you know.
I'm not a little
kid anymore, Mama.
Mama?
Can't you just listen to me?
You don't understand.
This place means a lot more
to me than I think you know.
I used to think that
perfecting a routine
was the most important thing,
but they taught me
that a good performance
is something you create
with an audience.
I was able to get back
the feelings I had
when I first started
doing diabolo.
And that's not all!
After I saw Sora and Layla do
the legendary great maneuver,
I felt like something
inside of me had opened up.
I want to be able to do that
kind of amazing show, too.
That's all I can think
about, all day long.
I can't stay quiet anymore.
Rosetta.
This time, I wanna become
like someone else.
I wanna be the one who
performs on stage with Sora.
I can even swing, watch me!
Rosetta!
Sora!
You're too reckless, Rosetta.
Sorry.
We're going back.
Okay.
My Rosetta. She's laughing.
Ta-da!
Thanks a lot, Sora.
Rosetta, I am afraid
of one thing, Rosetta.
That you're going to turn
into a machine all over again,
just like you did with diabolo.
You're very tough on yourself.
I know I was the one who trained
you hard when you were little,
but then, once you became
the youngest world
champion in history,
you aimed for even
more perfection,
and then you
developed a tendency
to drive yourself into corners.
Mama.
It's so tough to keep
watching you do that.
I'm the one who taught
you to be the very best.
But if you put yourself
back in that frame of mind,
I'm sure that you'll...
Mama.
It's true. When I
was a little girl,
you could be strict and
sometimes a little bit scary,
but I'm still really glad
that you taught me diabolo.
Don't worry, Mama.
I won't turn into a
machine again, I promise.
This'll be some hard training.
She'll go through
all kinds of feelings
and may even want
to cry sometimes.
She won't have time
to be a machine.
You're right.
After all, Kaleido
Stage is the place
that helped you
regain your smile.
Mr. Kalos, may I entrust
Rosetta to your care?
Of course you can.
But if she performs
diabolo for you,
I expect you to pay
her regular rate.
Huh? Right.
So does that mean you're going
to let me stay here, Mama?
Yes, you can stay here.
We did it!
Listen, I've got a ton of other
clients to attend to now,
so I'm going.
Call me if you need anything.
Mama.
I love you a lot, Mama!
That is so sweet.
Welcome to Kaleido Stage!
It's nice to meet you.
Hey, where's Sora?
She was just here a minute ago.
I saw her leave
with a piece of cake.
Who cares about
the welcome party?
I thought you might
want a piece of-
It doesn't matter which one.
Just satisfy me.
And so, Mia's new idea
for a show is 'Dracula!'
It's scary, but it's also
a passionate love story.
But May made a big fuss again,
saying that she deserved
to be Leon's partner.
There's only one day
left until the deadline.
Layla entrusted me
with her dream,
and I will never be
defeated. Never! Never!
Next time on Kaleido Star:
'The Amazing Passionate Rival.'
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky!