Hey, everyone,
Kaleido Star is about to start,
so make sure your room
is brightly lit and that
you're not sitting
too close to the TV.
My name is Sora Naegino.
Ever since I was a little girl
it's been my dream to
perform with Kaleido Stage.
So a few months ago I came
to the U.S. to give it a shot.
Boy, has it been an experience.
Everything is new to me,
and sometimes I'm little lost.
But that's not going to keep me
from doing my best.
There's nothing I can't
do if I try hard enough!
So, what would you do
if you were faced
with something super difficult?
When everybody around you said
there is no way
that you can do it.
But, in the end you just
gotta believe in yourself?
And change that that difficult
situation to an opportunity!
Change it! Change it!
A doll? A ghost? What is that?
You may call me Fool.
I am the sprit of the stage.
I can't hear you.
I'm not hearing any weird
voice. Nothing is there.
Nothing is there.
Oh, it's not there. Thank god.
What are you doing?
Listen, if you can see me,
it means that you
were chosen for the stage.
Oh no, it's still talking.
What is your name?
Sora Naegino... Why am
I talking back to it?!
It seems that tonight
a new star will be born.
It's the dawning of a new era
for the Kaleido Stage!
I'm asking for
a different room!
Hey!
Hmph!
My Amazing and
Lonely Challenge!
Excuse me, Dorm Supervisor,
may I come in?
Could you please ....!
Attack!
...explain what I just saw.
What's this?!
I, um... I'm sorry!
Teach me that trick
you just did!
What this?
Yes. I want you to teach me
this trick right now!
Oh, I didn't know
you're a new student.
Yes. My name is Sora Naegino.
Well, sorry, for what
I did out in the hall.
But you should never
open the door in the middle
of my karate practice.
Sorry, Dorm Supervisor,
but I uh...
By the way I'm Sarah, haha!
Sarah?... Sarah diva
of Kaleido Stage?
That's right.
So, this is the gorgeous Sarah,
I've heard so much about...
I can't believe it!
Hey, you are Japanese,
aren't you?
uh... um, yes.
I'm into Karate at the moment.
Can you be my sparring partner?
Everyone in Japan has
a Black Belt, right?
Oh, and teach me
that trick you just did, too.
And then...
you love Sushi right...?
Uh... I never knew Miss
Sarah was so, well...unique.
All that and I didn't
even get to change my room.
That's her, right?
The one who got in good with
the Boss and cheated her way in?
She was late for the
audition and still passed.
That makes me so mad.
She got in good with
the Boss to join the troupe?
I heard she's even sweet talked
her way onto the stage already.
That is unforgivable.
I had to try three times
before I got accepted
to the Kaleido Stage.
The third time's the charm, huh?
No.
Uh, I mean...
You mean?
I mean.. um,
"Better late than never?"
Yeah, thanks.
Shoot. I screwed up again.
Let's just forget it!
Not here. Looks like
it was just my imagination.
How weird...I guess I'm
more tired than I thought.
When you're tired,
you should take a shower
and go to bed early.
You're right.
I think I'll do that.
Take a shower and... huuuh?
Sora, go relax.
You're so uptight.
After all, it's been
a long day for you right?
Go now, Sora, into the shower.
Hum? See you look pale.
Go relax and then slumber
until the late morning hour.
Oh, he is still here.
How dare you treat the spirit
of the stage this way?!
I demand you to untie
this rope, right now.
Can you at least take off
this blindfold, please.
It's rather early
for that kind of work.
Oh, uh, Hello!
Newcomers don't usually clean
the place when they first start.
It's just I woke up
so early and...
Oh, I wanted to thank you
for allowing me to join
the Kaleido Stage.
Thank you very much.
Hum? Is something wrong?
You're a little on the
short side, but I think
you'll work out.
Oh, well that's nice.
Oh, good morning!
My, aren't we up bright
and early this morning?
Yeah, if you like
cleaning that much,
you can go ahead and all of
do ours while you're at it.
What?
Some of us really need
to get to our lesson early.
Oh yeah, I'm really talented,
but since I'm not close
to Kalos, the only way I can
appear on the stage is
by actually working hard.
So, you can take care of
the rest of cleaning for us.
Yeah, I feel better now.
That's all right.
I'll clean this myself. Aaah!
Just what you'd expect
from Kaleido Stage,
-- bigger than it looks.
Sora!
Huh? Ken.
Hey. You look tired.
What's going on?
It's just I didn't realize
it was too big of
a job for one person.
What! Did you clean
the stage by yourself?
Oh... No...
I meant I'm a slowpoke,
so it took me longer
than everyone else.
By the way,
if you don't hurry,
you will be late
for your lessons.
Oh, no. See you later!
Good luck, Sora. You still
have long road ahead of you.
Everyone,
please listen carefully!
In these ballet lessons,
I want you to master
how to move your body
beautifully which is essential
for performing
the grand ceremony.
A beautiful body movement,
is one that is...
Excuse me
I'm so sorry, I'm late!
Hum? What are you doing?!
Sorry, I'm late.
I was cleaning the stage.
Really... And weren't
you also late for the audition
the other day?
I apologize. I'll
try harder in future.
All right, fine. Now, we're
going to start today's lesson.
OK, everyone,
one row at a time, TURN!
I have to work harder.
Next!
Excuse me, you!
Oh, yes.
Don't you have any
ballet experience at all?
Uh... no.
Oh, dear. That just
will not do, at all!
You see, in order to present
a beautiful pose on the stage,
the knowledge of ballet
is absolutely essential.
E-sential!
That's all right.
OK people, I must
think... must think!
How did someone
like her ever get in?
It's so unfair!
Mm-hm.
She gets to make them laugh.
Oh... You're unbelievable...
I can't believe
you were on stage
when you couldn't do something
as easy as that turn.
Hmm?
Poor Sora. Can't make
a simple turn, but she'll
still get to go on stage.
It must be nice.
That's right...
Right now, I can't even make
a simple turn, but one day,
one day I will do great turns.
And someday,
I'll do amazing routines,
just like Layla does....
Uh, Just like Layla...
the Golden Phoenix?
Ha, you're kidding; you think
the Golden Phoenix is that easy?
You think it's a piece of cake?
Well... I didn't mean like that.
Go ahead then... Why don't
show us your Golden Phoenix?
Oh... no... well...
Doing the Golden Phoenix
must be a piece of cake for you
since Kalos has such great
confidence in your abilities.
I just meant...
What's wrong?
Can't you do that?
I'll let you know that I don't
acknowledge that you are here.
You don't belong on the stage.
All right then. I will do it!
I will show you that
I can do the Golden Phoenix!
Really? I will
look forward to it.
Then, be ready
to show it to me in a week.
But, if you can't do it
after claiming so boldly
that you could, I will ask
you to leave here immediately.
Fine.
Yuri, let's go
to the training room.
It isn't like you
to say something
like that to a newcomer.
I just can't stand that
Kalus would let someone
on Kaleido Stage who
cannot do anything.
The Golden Phoenix?!
I'd like to borrow a video
of Miss Layla if you have it.
That is totally reckless!
The Golden Phoenix is
a trick that only Miss Layla,
the top star is
capable of doing!
I know.
And it's a maneuver
that is done on the swings.
Sora, have you ever
worked on swings before?
No, but I've got no choice,
I have to do it!
I want everyone to accept me.
And for that, I have no choice,
but do the Golden Phoenix!
Sora...
The Golden Phoenix
is a trick that you
swing the swings widely,
and spin your body
with a high speed.
Then release the bar
and fly towards your
partner like a phoenix
with your arms wide open
and catch your partner's bar.
The spinning of your body
using this special bar
is extremely difficult.
Layla and Yuri are
using the training room
for their new routine.
So, you have to use
the actual swings on the stage.
It has a net, but it's
still pretty dangerous
since we're so high up.
I'll be all right.
So, what I need to do?
Well... First, you need to
practice to sway your body
side and side.
Then, you will jump to
the bar on the other side
after you gain enough momentum.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
If you fall, make sure you
land on your back. All right?
You don't have enough
momentum! Just let go! Whew.
I never knew just
swinging was this hard.
But, I will do it
no matter what!
I'm sorry that I ended up
keeping you here until morning.
Oh, don't worry about it.
If it's for you, I don't...
Sora!
Mr. Policeman!
What are you doing
so early in the morning?
I was practicing the swings.
I see, well good luck. Tell me
when you will be on stage, okay?
I am your fan No.1, you got it?
Oh, thank you, very much.
Hm? Hmm.
H- Hi...
I'll test you
to see if you're a man
worthy of being
Sora's boyfriend or not!
You got it all wrong!
He is not my boyfriend; he's
not anything at all... !
You sure?
No, Not at all...
Good luck Sora!
Not anything at all like that...
I really better
work hard though...
Or I'll end up
having to leave this place
before I ever get on
the Kaleido stage.
Ken... meet me later
tonight, too, okay?
Of course.
Oh...
Were you practicing
all this time?
Yes, because if I don't
work hard at it...
It's not something you can do,
just by working hard at it.
Why don't you give up
and apologize to Layla?
No, I'm not giving up.
I gave up once on joining
Kaleido Stage because
I missed the audition.
But, somehow I managed to get
in. So, I want to stay here!
I don't ever want
to give up on it again!
Ow...
If you think that's painful, the
road will be a long one for you.
Oh... He is still here.
The upside down "Chariot."
This card indicates that
things will end in failure
and that you will taste defeat.
Sora, the results of a
fortune telling may be bad,
but the future
can be changed...
Huh?
...but it depends
on that person's efforts.
In order to have muscle
strength to be able to perform
these kinds of acrobatics,
you have to eat low fat
and high protein foods.
Check her out...
She really must
be working hard..
I did it!
Okay, Sora. Next, you have to
do it while you're spinning.
Sora!
Huh?
We brought you something!
We know you haven't
eaten anything.
Oh...
How do you like it?
It's really good.
You need the protein;
eat it all, okay?
Mmm-hm
And I recommend you try this.
Hot Pepper drink?
It will give you energy.
Anna, Mia, thank you.
Sorry, Sora. I should have
never mentioned something
like the Golden
Phoenix to you...
Don't worry about that.
Now I have the chance
to prove myself around here.
At first, I thought
you were accepted
because you got in good
with the Boss.
But I guess that wasn't
the really case.
Sorry for being hard on you.
It's okay-no big deal..
Oh, the Band-Aid on
your hand is coming loose.
Here, I'll fix it. for you.
Good luck.
We're rooting for you.
Thank you.
Swing the bar side to side,
and spin. Then jump.
Is Sora okay?
She is doing
visualization training.
She is picturing the image
of the perfected
routine in her head.
Hm.
And Finish.
Therefore... Well...
In other words...
I'm listening to the
lecture. So, just go on.....
Yes, Thank you ...
Oh, Yuri?!
Where on earth are you
looking when you jump?
Huh?
There is no Juliet who is not
always looking for her Romeo.
That's why you
cannot be Juliet.
Oh... but... Yuri...
I am just trying
to get the golden phoenix;
I wasn't trying for Juliet.
Oh, that was
close wasn't it..
I can't believe
she's really doing it.
If only she could
grab that bar...
No, not yet. She still
can't keep a beautiful pose
in the air. Even before
she catches the bar,
what she is doing can't
be called the Golden Phoenix.
Go, Sora!
By tomorrow... It has to
be perfect it by tomorrow.
You couldn't perfect it after
all, but you did your best.
Who knows?
The real test is tomorrow.
I haven't given up
hope just yet.
So why have you given up Ken.
I cannot wait to see
what kind of Golden Phoenix
she is going to show us.
I know.
Thank you all for coming.
I've got to do it.
Uhh. I must believe!
The one I need to aim for is
not the bar. My aim is my love,
My aim is Romeo.
And then, then I'll be Juliet.
The Golden Phoneix!
She did it!
Oh...
Oh!
Sora, are you all right?
Yes. Thank you.
You're really something.
Oh... uh Layla.
You didn't get
the last part right,
but it was definitely
the Golden Phoenix.
Huh?!
You definitely deserve
credit for pulling it off.
Yuri, let's go.
Sora, you can stay here
at Kaleido Stage!
--Congratulations, Sora!
--I'm so glad for you, Sora!
Oh...
That so cool.
I can stay at Kaleido Stage?
Cheers!
Aren't you happy that able
to stay at Kaleido Stage, Sora?
Yes, of course I am.
You're still here?!
Sora, I think you should
all fly a kite together;
they say real friendship begins
when you all fly a kite.
But thats just
my friends I suppose.
That's enough!
Ouch! What are
you doing, Sora?!
Oh, well... This is... Um...
Well... Please stop it!
Hmm?
Oh... oops!
I know what this is...
This is that Japanese comedy
routine called "Tsukkomi" isn't
it? I've heard of this before.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
Um...Hey, you guys
cannot really see him?
See who?
Oh...
What a party? Oh no,
no girls - not good.
Dorm Supervisor!
So, parties aren't allowed?
Of course, not...
unless you invite me .
Because those are
the rules at this dormitory.
Miss Sarah...
Miss Sarah?!
No way!
Now, let's have some fun!
Unbelievable!
You don't have a role.
Kaleido Stage's
next theme is Cinderella.
I heard that
all of the newcomer's
will participant in this.
But, I'm only one
who doesn't have a role?
It can't be.
It must be some
kind of mistake.
According to the roster Kalos,
my job as handing out toys to
children in the theater. Um...
I just make it here!
Gotta! Gotta!
Next Kaleido Star,
"The Amazing Distant Stage!"
My wings are my dreams
and on toward the sky...