Hey, everyone, Kaleido
Star's about to start,
so make sure that your room
is brightly lit and that you're
not sitting too close to the TV.
Well, well, well, isn't it
so exciting doing something
for the first time?
My heart starts racing
just thinking about it!
This is my first leading role
ever and I'm trying my best,
but somehow I still end up
getting in trouble.
I just don't know what I'm
doing wrong! I don't, I don't!
Sora Naegino here
will be the Mermaid.
Anna Heart will play the Prince.
'The Little Mermaid' will
be presented by Kenneth in
a special two-week limited
engagement. We hope you enjoy
seeing these up-and-comers
prove themselves.
What's it like to have
your first leading part?
What do you think about Layla's
move to the silver screen?
Let's see, tomorrow you've got
a photo shoot for the posters
and then you've got
a newspaper interview.
Next day you've got another
photo shoot, then you're on TV.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing. It's just, I still
can't believe this is happening.
Snap out of it. You've got a lot
of work to do, leading lady.
Leading lady...
'Facing an Amazing Wall.'
Sora!
Get your head out of the clouds!
I-- I'm sorry.
We've gotta pose for the
posters. Just follow directions.
Mermaid, I need you to
look a little more lively.
Uh, sure.
Great. And, Prince,
get closer, would you?
Okay, guys, show me the romance.
How about this?
Perfect!
Anna looked so handsome as the
prince. I was so embarrassed...
You both look great!
You really think so?
Don't you like it?
I was kinda hoping I'd look
more like a jellyfish...
Anyway, you guys
are gonna be great.
You think so?
They'd better hope they're good.
If I was doing those roles
I wouldn't have to
hope for success.
Don't listen to them!
You and Anna are way more
talented than they'll ever be!
Oh I've got too much
other stuff to worry about,
like how to play the part
as well as Layla did.
I have to be perfect!
Sora! You have a phone call!
A phone call?
This is Sora.
Oh hi, Mom! Huh? Yes.
Well, we're remounting the show
for two weeks and guess
what? I'm the lead!
I know. I will be.
You shouldn't worry so much.
Love you, too.
Thanks, Ken.
I'll bet your folks
are really proud of you.
Yeah. But they're
so worried about me.
You mean because they
think you'll overdo it
since this is your
first starring role?
What other choice do I have?
I'm playing a part
that Layla made famous.
I've gotta work harder
than I ever have!
Ken, did you bring that for me?
Oh that's right.
I almost forgot.
Excellent! Now I can watch
Layla's Little Mermaid over
and over again.
I'm gonna memorize
this tape! Thank you, Ken!
Happy to help. After all, I
wanna see you do well with --
See you later, bye!
Oh, Layla's even better
in this than I remembered,
so beautiful and graceful...
And the audience is so
moved that they're weeping.
That's the thing about this
production -- it's supposed to
make you feel like crying.
I wish I could perform
just like she does.
What're you doing?!
You seem almost giddy today.
But can you afford to be?
What?
The inverted Magician. This
card means that you will lose
everything unless you commit
yourself to the task at hand--
I'm trying to watch this.
You know, it would be nice if
you paid some attention to me
every once in a while.
Go for it Sora!
Can't believe we're opening...
You guys, we're
completely sold out!
Really? Good. I was
afraid no one would come
since Layla's not
in it this time.
Sora! I'm counting on you.
Yes, sir!
Wow. She's wonderful.
She's more graceful than
I thought she could be.
No way...
She's just like Layla.
Sora...
Sora, that was beautiful!
Just beautiful!
Cheers!
Didn't she do a fantastic job?
Yeah, Sora should be
really proud of herself.
Where is she, anyway?
Uh still on stage, I guess.
It's too bad she's missing this,
especially since you planned
this great party for her debut.
No big deal. That just
means more food for us!
Miss Sarah, you can eat
more than anyone I know.
I'll give a performance tomorrow
that touches their hearts
just like Layla's did.
Oh no...
I don't get it.
How come the audience
is so much smaller today?
And after we gave such
a perfect show yesterday.
I mean, even our most difficult
routines were totally spot-on.
Hey, have you seen Sora?
It's Sora.
Come in.
Okay, Boss.
Mr. Kenneth?
Let's cut to the chase: her
performance stunk yesterday.
I'd never have replaced Layla if
I'd known she'd be this bad.
I guess it serves me right
for trying something new...
Wait, Mr. Kenneth. I know
my performance isn't as good
as Layla's, no one knows that
better than I do, but I'm still
working and it and I promise
I won't let you down, sir.
Oh, this is useless.
You don't even know why I'm
disappointed in you, do you?
Kalos. Get Layla
back here quick.
But she's in the middle
of filming for her movie,
remember, sir?
Then get her back here
once she's done with
her blasted movie!
Mr. Kenneth please,
I can do this part!
I'm sorry, Sora, but
the producer has spoken.
Sora?
Ken are those the
audience questionnaires?
Yeah.
Let me see!
'You had a new mermaid this
time, but she was wonderful
just like Layla was.'
'The production was nice.
It looks like you've found
the next Layla Hamilton.
Your beautiful new set made
me wish I could see Layla
perform in it.'
They didn't write
anything negative,
they just wanted Layla back.
Your Little Mermaid's
technically very good, Sora,
but it just doesn't move people.
But why not? I'm doing
everything Layla did.
I-- I've studied her tape
a hundred times and--
Sora you're not Layla.
This card means that you
will lose everything unless
you commit yourself
to the task at hand.
That's it. That's what
he was talking about.
The world doesn't
need two Laylas...
The show's about to start.
Get to places.
I can't do this.
What?
I can't. How can I perform when
I know I'm not going to be
any good? And I don't have any
idea how I can make it better.
Well whether you know or not, we
have to start the show. Come on!
You're the leading lady, Sora!
Was it necessary to be
so hard on her, Ken?
All the new leads they face
this same kind of wall.
I know she's scared and
confused, but unless she can
get past that and do the work,
she'll never be able to create
a role that's all her own.
This isn't working.
What can I do?
I just-- I just don't know...
Sora, we're leaving.
Come on.
I'm sorry. I was a mess
out there. I know it.
That doesn't make the
audience any happier, does it?
Anna!
They didn't come all the way
out here to see that half-baked
performance you gave today.
I want you to
stop messing around
and get serious with this.
But I...
You and I are
gonna figure this out:
how to create
your Little Mermaid.
How to create
my Little Mermaid...
Oh, this is useless.
You don't even know why I'm
disappointed in you, do you?
That's right Sora!
You'll do a show like
they've never seen before!
Like they've never seen...
Yeah, thanks for
your help, you guys.
Come on, let's get to work.
You're right.
Everyone has to be able to
sympathize with the Mermaid.
And if I don't know
what she's going through,
how can I expect
other people to?
So... how are you going
to connect with that?
First of all,
you need to know what it
feels like to be a mermaid.
But how does that feel?
Oh!
You got an idea?
Sora!
Sora?
I'll think about it
while I'm in the water.
After all,
that's where she'd be.
I wonder if Sora is
starting to understand.
Anyway, she's got to eat...
Yeah!
Sora!
Here ya go!
Wha?
Hey, Ken.
Don't 'hey' me! Sora, what do
you think you're doing?
You can't afford to
play around right now!
But that's what mermaids do.
The sea is beautiful and
it's their home, so they get
to swim in it all day long.
And they don't have to work.
She's right.
And there's never anyone who
yells or is mean to them...
That's got nothing
to do with this!
Someone who's lived
like this all her life...
I'd imagine someone like
that would be pretty cheerful
and sure of herself,
don't you think?
The Little Mermaid's
a tragic heroine.
How can she be
those things, too?
Well, I guess I'll never know
unless I give it a shot.
Oh no. The Little Mermaid's
not supposed to make the
audience laugh at her...
Looks like she finally
cracked under all that pressure
and lost her mind, huh?
What is she thinking?
Thank you for coming out
today. Drive safely.
Yeah, thanks for coming!
Sora?
Excuse me,
would you mind telling me
what you thought of the show?
Huh?
Please, I wanna know
your honest opinion.
What are you doing?
Well, I thought she was kinda
cute how you played her.
Yeah, but why would someone
so self-assured just give up
in the end? It didn't
make any sense.
He's right. When Layla Hamilton
played the Mermaid she was
more graceful and refined,
so her sacrifice made sense.
Hey, thanks for your input.
Now if you'll excuse us...
What were you thinking cornering
audience members like that?
How else am I supposed
to know if it's working?
I just can't watch myself
the way the audience can.
Then ask one of us--
That's right, what did
you think of it today.
It was pretty different from
Layla's performance, wasn't it?
Well I guess you could
say it shows more of
your personality now...
Yeah, and?
And I prefer it to what
you were doing before...
Hey, Sora.
What the heck do you
think you were doing?
That's not the Little Mermaid
from rehearsals.
You can't just change the show
whenever you feel like it,
you know.
Before you change anything,
you get permission from me.
I'm sorry I upset you all.
I was just trying to make
this Mermaid my own.
Why are you even bothering with
that? The show runs two weeks.
Look, just do it like we
rehearsed it, all right?
Sora?
Sorry. We never meant to get
you into trouble with them.
I should've known it would
just confuse people.
No. This is not your fault.
It's all mine.
You weren't wrong to try. Seems
like the problem is no one knows
who your Mermaid's
supposed to be.
What...
I mean, you just started
public performances.
If they'd just give you time to
figure this out you'd be fine.
You're right. It's not
'only two weeks.'
I've got two whole weeks.
I've gotta use this time.
I've got to make this
Little Mermaid all my own.
But, Sora...
Hey. What the heck is this?
Oh, I figured I'd live like
the Little Mermaid as long as
the show's on.
Huh?
I finally faced up to the
fact I'm not the same kind of
performer that Layla is.
And so I'm gonna have to find
my own version of this
character from the inside out.
Sora!
Hey, are you all right?
Don'tcha think you're
taking this too far?
I bet you've cut off the
circulation in your feet
wearing those fins all the time.
That's right! She's
had fins all her life,
so when she gets legs
I'll bet she falls down a lot--
it takes her a long time to
learn how to walk with them!
I've been trying to get
inside the Mermaid's head,
to figure out what
she's feeling, but there's
still something I don't get.
What is it?
She loves the Prince, right?
She loves him so much that
she trades in her voice so she
can be human and be with him.
But if that's true, then why
didn't she tell him how she felt
when he got engaged
to that other girl?
But how can she tell him that?
She doesn't have a voice.
She'd still try to let him know.
If she felt that
strongly about him, I mean.
If I were her there's no way I'd
just give up without a fight.
I'd find some way to
let him know how I felt.
But without her voice...
Maybe the rest of
the cast'll have an idea.
So you're asking why the Little
Mermaid withdraws herself?
Yes. I mean, if she's supposed
to love the Prince so much how
can she just let him go like
that? She might not be able
to talk, but she can
still fight for him!
Hmm. That's an interesting
point your making,
but it's not in
our script, Sora.
Maybe that's why: the
audience can't identify
with her because she just
rolls over and plays dead
instead of fighting for him.
Yeah. Then maybe we can add
a scene where she tries as hard
as she can to get
through to him.
Maybe she could even fight
a duel with his fiancée.
That's a great idea!
But still the Prince
can't remember her.
Would she admit defeat then?
No, she'd hold the Prince's hand
and jump into
the ocean with him.
Have the Prince jump
into the waterfall?
How else can she remind him?
Anna, that's wonderful!
The Mermaid takes the
Prince back to the ocean.
And then the Prince finally
remembers that it was her
who saved him!
A happy ending!
It's perfect!
This story's always been
played as a tragedy before!
I think this'll be a
much better production
if it's got a happy ending.
Looks like this is gonna
turn out to be a pretty
interesting show.
I'm gonna run all this by Kalos,
and if he approves we'll start
rehearsing again tomorrow!
It's me.
Come in, Layla.
So I finished the filming early.
Mr. Kenneth called me about
coming back and doing the show.
I hear Sora tried playing
the part my way once,
and then started making
some pretty radical changes.
I guess she's not ready to play
a leading role yet, is she?
I think you should see the show.
Over half these seats are empty.
No wonder Mr. Kenneth
was complaining. Kalos?
What is she doing?
She's testing to see whether
the Sea Witch really
has magic powers or not.
Why'd she do that?
Because the Sea Witch
could just be lying to her.
That is totally absurd.
Keep watching it
to the end, okay?
What's that blue ribbon? Is that
supposed to symbolize the waves?
Oh, she wants him
to remember her.
She did it, she did it!
That's what I was hoping for,
the kind of Kaleido Star that
no one's ever seen before!
That girl playing the
Mermaid was awesome!
Yeah, she was really funny!
I never thought
I'd enjoy watching
'The Little Mermaid'
this much!
Great job!
They really seemed to like it!
And I enjoyed
performing it today, too!
It was awesome!
Sora--
Great show!
Hey, Sora! I've got a new
idea for the ballroom scene,
mind if I run it past you?
All right.
I was thinking of turning
the starfish into
something different, too.
I've gotta hand it to her,
she made the show her own...
She's turned into a leading
lady right before our eyes.
She's incredible, isn't she?
In this production,
even the supporting cast
seems energized and excited.
Maybe it's because they
were given unconventional
new characters to play. At any
rate, I think Kaleido Stage
has got a new title: 'The Little
Mermaid Who Makes Her Own Way.'
Junk Baron. That's the
perfect stage name for me.
You remember that Anna's father
is a standup comedian, right?
Well, we all decided to see his
show when he was in town, but--
That man's not my father!
He's nothing like
the Dad Anna remembers
from when she was little.
I feel like I've gotta
keep her memories of him
from being ruined.
I've gotta, I've gotta!
Next time on Kaleido Star:
'Anna's not-so-amazing Father.'
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...