Hey, everyone,
Kaleido Star's about to start,
so make sure your room
is brightly lit and that you're
not sitting too close to the TV.
My name is Sora Naegino.
Ever since I was a little girl
it's been my dream
to perform with Kaleido Stage.
So a few months ago I came
to the U.S. to give it a shot.
Boy, has it been an experience.
Everything is new to me,
and sometimes I'm a little lost.
But that's not going to keep me
from doing my best.
There's nothing I can't do
if I work hard!
Well, well, well.
Do you tell your Mom and Dad
your true feelings about stuff
like what you dream of doing?
Of course, I don't wanna
make my parents worry,
but I don't want
any regrets either.
I wish I could tell them
how I really feel, y'know?
Y'know? Y'know? Y'know?
'My Amazingly Distant Family'.
It's fifteen minutes
'til curtain, folks.
Was your grandmother's
surgery okay?
I called few minutes ago.
Everything's fine.
I'm so glad.
Huh? Thanks, Anna.
How do you
like my new nose job?
Gimme those things.
Oh come on, if I can't make this
Fairy Godmother thing funny
I'm gonna explode!
Back me up here, Sora.
Great. She's not even listening.
Too busy getting ready
for your second
Kaleido Stage triumph, huh?
Maybe not...
Sora?
Miss Sarah?
She sure cleans up
pretty good, doesn't she?
Hey! I always look this nice!
She really needs to get
better with those nun chucks.
Excuse me, Officer,
where is Kaleido Stage?
Kaleido Stage, huh?
Uh, I-- yes.
Are you Japanese?
I am.
You're a lucky man.
You got here just in time
to see Japan's finest
performer make her debut.
Who's performing?
My friend Sora.
That's my daughter.
Come here!
Uh. No thanks.
Ladies and gentlemen, prepare
yourselves to be swept away.
The performance will
begin in a few moments.
The three of us
have to be perfect today.
Right. Let's do this.
There's not an empty seat in the
house. Break a leg, you guys.
It's a full house?
I uh didn't mean
to freak you guys out...
Everybody gets nervous
on opening day you know.
Even her? But Layla's
done this a million times.
Remember you made it into the
show by the skin of your teeth,
so don't you let me down.
Right.
I appreciate it, but you really
don't have to escort me there.
Of course I do, Big Daddy.
You can't miss Sora's show.
It's amazing how
comfortable she looks on stage.
Then again, opening a show
is nothing new to her anymore.
But she's better than
she was in rehearsal.
It's like the audience brought
something new out of her.
And we've gotta be
even better to match her.
The Fairy Godmother routine
starts as soon as Sarah
finishes her song.
Are you guys ready?
Let's do our best.
If we do that, there's no way
we can fail. Am I right?
Let's go.
It's Sora...
You can do this.
Remember to watch your timing.
All right!
So far so good! Now it's
time for the tricky part--
the Triple Illusion.
Oh no! I was late!
I'm on.
But they haven't...
They messed up,
now gimme some effects.
Okay got it.
Miss Layla?
She's covering our mistake.
Sora!
Sit down! I'm trying
to watch the show!
Smile, idiot!
Let them see you're okay!
I'm so sorry, boss.
It's my fault.
My timing was completely off
So Sora here couldn't
stay on her feet because
your timing was off?
I'm so sorry. You would've
been fine if I hadn't messed up.
No, Mia. Kalos was right:
I shouldn't have been thrown
by Miss Layla's entrance.
Sora! Someone's here to see you!
What?
Sora.
Dad it's you!
You you're Sora's father?
Uh, you don't think he's here
to make her go home, do you?
He wasn't too happy about her
coming here in the first place,
so you could be right.
It's good to see you.
How rude of me! These are
my friends, Anna and Mia.
It's nice to make
your acquaintance.
Uh, thank you...
Why didn't you tell me you
were coming. Did Mom come, too?
Uh no. I came by myself.
It's a business trip.
I wish she could've come.
Yes. She worries about you
being so far away.
She shouldn't worry...
Uh, excuse me...
Dad, this is Ken.
I thought you might be thirsty.
So I brought you some soda.
I'm so glad you got
to see me perform today.
But I wish I'd
done a better job.
Huh? Oh, this? That's
just one of my battle scars.
Sora--
What?
Oh... noth--.
Nothing. Nothing at all.
So... It's too bad
you're leaving so soon.
I wish I had time to do
some sightseeing with you.
Maybe next time. Oh. I know.
Why don't you and I
have a nice dinner?
There's a Japanese
restaurant at my hotel.
I don't know.
I have a long practice
with Anna and Mia tonight...
One hour.
Right. I mean,
I'll have to eat anyway.
I might as well eat
with you while you're here.
Don't worry about it.
Well. Practice hard.
Okay.
Uh, Dad? Are you
coming back tomorrow?
Ah, yes. I think I see now.
The people you call 'Mom and
Dad' aren't your real parents.
Sora! Sora please!
My hair is caught!
Dad came all this way
just to see me.
I'm not gonna let him down.
Oh, this is terrible!
Now everyone has to
suffer for their mistakes.
Good morning, you guys.
That wasn't very nice.
I wonder what their problem is.
It's a review of
yesterday's performance.
"In Kaleido Stage's new
production of 'Cinderella,'
Layla Hamilton
shines once more.
The only major misstep of the
evening was in casting three
obvious amateurs
in the demanding role
of the Fairy Godmother."
I almost wish we'd been fired.
There's no way we can recover
from a review like that.
Mia. Just forget about it.
What are you doing?
Oh boss...
This isn't about that review
in the newspaper, is it?
I can cover for your mistakes,
so stop moping and get
your heads in the game.
Mia and Anna aren't jumping
as high as they were yesterday.
Hey, aren't those Fairy
Godmother people the ones
that got a terrible review
in the paper this morning?
Yeah. They almost
make Layla look bad.
Right this way, Mr. Naegino.
What were you
thinking out there?
If you can't do better
than that you have no business
being on stage.
This is an important scene.
If you can't do it, resign.
We're sorry, Miss Layla.
I can't believe
they did it again.
I know! Poor Layla...
Sora?
Can I talk to you?
Sora, come back home.
What?
Come back to Japan.
But, Dad...
To tell you the truth,
I came out here to check on you.
Your mother is very
worried about you.
She and I agreed that if you
weren't doing well out here
I'd bring you home.
I'm sorry to say this, Sora,
but I just... I don't think...
I don't think that
Kaleido Stage is where
you need to be right now.
I should never have allowed
you to come in the first place.
Such a dangerous job. Besides,
I can't stand to think of you
having such a
hard time over here.
Sora, you're getting out of
this place. I'm won't get on
that plane tomorrow unless
you agree to come with me.
What?
Sora!
You were gone for so long
we thought you'd run away.
You okay?
Yeah. You guys are
sweet to worry about me.
What did your Dad
wanna tell you?
Uh...
What's wrong?
He wants me to return
with him... to Japan.
What did you say? You're
not going, are you? Well?
What else can I do?
I want to stay,
but they're so worried
about me. I can't hurt them.
I know we can't replace them.
But we'll always
be here for you, Sora.
My biological parents
died when I was very young.
I hadn't even started
primary school yet.
I've never felt so abandoned.
My father's cousin and his
wife took me in and raised me
as their own daughter.
Do you think maybe that's
why he doesn't understand
how you feel about this place?
I mean, if he's
not your real Dad...
He is now. He and my
mother are great parents,
and I know they'd
do anything for me.
They've always had
my best interests at heart.
How could I tell them
I don't want to go home?
So you're lying to them? Nice
way of showing your gratitude.
Hey, are you okay?
Sora, something awful has
happened to you-- your Dad!
What?
He's had a heart attack!
A heart attack?!
The police just called to let
us know. The paramedics took him
to Cape Mary Hospital
on 9th street.
But the show starts in an hour.
We're supposed to be
backstage in ten minutes.
Sora! Oh, no...
If I don't show up for the show
I'm gonna be fired for sure.
But I can't go on
if he's in danger.
I'll bet Miss Layla
would've gone on anyway.
She would've been able to
perform like nothing was wrong.
She's a real professional.
I guess I'll never be...
Dad! Are you okay?
Sora...
Dad, I I'll do it.
I'll leave Kaleido Stage
and go back with you to Japan.
Sora...
I wouldn't be able
to forgive myself if
something happened to you
while I was away.
But I...
It's okay.
What on earth was
that girl thinking?
She's worried about her father.
We all have worries, but
none of us are missing a show.
We'll find someone else
who can do it.
With five minutes to
curtain? I don't think so.
Layla, you cover for her.
They must've started by now.
Wait!
Came back, did you?
I'm so sorry.
And you think that
makes everything okay?
It doesn't. I just wanted
to tell you I'm quitting.
I'm surprised. I thought
it would take more than
a disappointment to make
you give up your dream.
I wonder if she's serious.
You sound disappointed.
But you don't want to quit.
Maybe you should
sleep on it, Sora.
I'm sorry,
but I've already decided.
But we can't do the
Triple Illusion without you.
If you talk to Kalos,
I'm sure he'll let you back in.
You can find someone else
to do the routine.
But I'm the only daughter
that my Mom and Dad
are ever gonna have.
And you know what,
I'm happy. I got to perform
with Kaleido Stage, even if
it was just for a little while.
The Moon represents
wavering emotions.
But when the clouds clear,
your indecision will vanish.
Are you sure
you're okay to fly Dad?
As long as you're with me
Sora, I can do anything.
Thanks.
Hey, Dad?
Hm?
I wanted to ask you how
you liked Kaleido Stage.
Because you hadn't been before.
It was nice.
Don't you think
Layla's amazing? And Yuri?
I still can't believe I got
the chance to perform
with the two of them.
I mean, when I came for the
audition, I never dreamed
I'd get in. Then I did.
And you and Mom were so
supportive even though I knew
you hated the thought
of me being so far away.
But you supported me anyway.
I wish that you'd come on a
different day that you'd seen
a better performance.
Where I didn't mess up.
I'm sorry you never got to see
the Triple Illusion the way
we practiced it.
Because it's really kinda
cool when we do it right.
Sora...
I'm just really disappointed.
And I... I don't... I don't
want to quit Kaleido Stage.
I've dreamed of
being on stage there
as long as I can remember, Dad.
But I don't want
to hurt you and Mom.
Sora. I'm going.
But you should stay here.
You should have told me how
you felt about this before.
Your mother and
I want to protect you,
we don't want
to make you unhappy.
But, Dad...
Take care of yourself Sora.
Dad?
Thank you, Dad.
I'm so sorry.
I don't want to quit
Kaleido Stage. I never did.
Please, give me another chance.
I won't make any more mistakes.
I promise!
That's fine, but we're
not the only people
you should be apologizing to.
Ever since we've opened,
none of our audiences have seen
what the Fairy
Godmothers can do yet.
They deserve your
best performance.
Right!
Someday I want my Mom
and Dad to see me perform
when everything goes like
it should. I can't wait!
Oh my gosh. I found a seal!
Huh?
I'll call him Jonathan.
But, Sora, we're not
allowed to keep any pets.
And how are you
going to feed it?
That's gonna
take money, you know.
Well, why don't we take part
in a juggling contest.
We can feed him with
the money we win! Okay?
Okay.
Next time on Kaleido Star,
'The Amazing Seal.'
My wings are my dream,
and on towards the sky...