Well, well, well.
Has anyone out there ever had
to keep a really big secret?
If you have, then you
know it's not easy.
I mean, I promised I wouldn't
say anything, but I'm feeling
kind of bad about having
to keep secrets from people
I really care about.
Now I understand how Layla must
feel. I do, I do, I really do!
Looks like we can't perform
again. The afternoon show's off.
I'm glad to have
you kids aboard.
Thanks to your show, my park
has more visitors than ever.
I just wanted to
show my appreciation.
Please, I want you to
eat as much as you like!
All right!
I never thought he'd be
this generous of a person.
I guess you can't judge
a book by its cover, eh?
It has nothing
to do with generosity.
If we're well fed,
we'll do better shows.
I always knew you were
a sharp one, Rosetta.
Yeah, real sharp.
But why isn't the Masked Star
joining us for dinner today?
I think she told me she, uh,
had to go to a sickle
and chain workshop.
A sickle and chain..?
Sorry she couldn't make it.
Maybe next time.
'The Amazing Resolve
Beneath the Mask.'
You've received a
bouquet, Miss Layla.
I wonder if it's from your fan
who refuses to believe
that you're in London.
It's from Yuri.
What?
Are you enjoying hide-and-seek?
Miss Layla, you'll
be late for your flight.
And if you don't
catch the six o'clock,
you'll never make it in time
for filming tomorrow.
I almost forgot.
Let's get going.
I assume you've received
and reviewed the picture
I sent to you.
There's no doubt that
the Masked Star is Layla.
My daughter is busy
filming a movie in London.
It can't be her.
How can you be
so sure of that?
You know, Yuri,
I hear that Kaleido Stage's
attendance is slipping,
and perhaps you're
having trouble
covering your bottom line.
Even so, it's pretty pathetic
that you would stoop to this.
Well... Sooner or later,
you're gonna find out the truth.
We'll be arriving at Heathrow
Airport shortly, Mr. Hamilton.
And cut!
Fantastic! That was
incredible, Layla!
I'd like to see how
the shot turned out.
It's my Father!
So, are you in
London for business?
Yes. I'd been planning to come
to one of your little shoots,
so this was the
perfect opportunity.
How is it going, Layla?
Mr. Hamilton, you're not
worried that I'm working
your darling daughter
mercilessly, are you?
Of course not, she'll work as
hard as you feel is necessary.
He knows me too well.
Well we're glad
to have you here.
A friend of yours called me this
afternoon with some nonsense
about you performing
in an amusement park.
Who did you hear that from?
No, let me guess: Yuri Killian.
Oh, don't be worried about silly
rumors like that, sweetheart.
Just part of being a star.
So, is Dio off today, too?
I think he's got an
afternoon performance
with Theatrical Camp.
Right, when you've got a roof,
it doesn't matter whether
it rains or shines.
If the rain keeps
coming down like this,
maybe we'll end up
having the whole week off!
Well, if it does keep
raining, we're gonna have
a company meeting so we can come
up with some new show ideas.
You mean we'll have to work?
Yes, I understand.
But we can talk about a more
detailed schedule later.
Rosetta.
If you need to go back home
to take care of your other
engagements, we'll understand.
I know I can go home, I'm
here 'cause I wanna be here.
Don't worry about me, Sora, I've
got everything under control.
I'm glad you're here.
You wanna buy 2,000 admission
tickets to my park per day?!
I'd like to do a promotion
at Kaleido Stage where
we give tickets to the
Marine Park to our patrons.
In order to make this work
I'm going to need 2,000 tickets
per day for the entire summer.
That means I'll need one hundred
eighty thousand tickets.
And I'd like to buy them now.
That's a lot of tickets...
Looks like this is going
to be a rainy month.
As an owner whose business
is affected by the weather,
I don't have to tell you that
this is a dream come true.
But-- and correct me
if I'm wrong--
aren't we Kaleido
Stage's biggest rivals?
This sale doesn't come
with provisions, does it?
It does. I'll buy
under one condition only:
That you cancel Freedom Lights'
performances and nullify
their contract with the park.
But Freedom Lights
is the biggest draw
we've ever had here.
No one would ever bother to come
if they weren't performing.
That's true even without
the Masked Star, is it?
She may not be back.
Or hadn't they told you that?
No, no need to worry.
I'm glad to hear that the
filming is going so smoothly.
This movie's success is
extremely important, Layla,
it could make or
break your career.
That's why I selected
this project so carefully
and assembled the best
possible cast and crew.
Yes, I understand, Father.
If we keep on schedule,
we should be filming your final
fight scenes by next week.
I'm looking forward
to seeing them.
Thank you.
Looks like she isn't coming...
She what?! The Masked Star
didn't show up today?!
That Mr. Killian
warned me about this...
We're fired?
You can't do that! We
have a binding contract!
That contract is
worthless! You lied to me.
You knew I was more interested
in that masked performer
than any of you.
Now I find out she's not
even part of your company.
I'm so glad that nice Yuri
Killian informed me of this.
Yuri said..?
You heard me. Now all of you
get off my property.
Yuri did this?
Stupid Yuri.
I never thought
he could stoop so low...
Well, from what I hear,
Kaleido Stage isn't doing
as well as he had hoped.
Freedom Lights is
too much competition.
So do a better job.
We'd never have been a threat
without the Masked Star.
You think so?
We've got to figure out how to
put on a great show without her.
So what is
everyone gonna do now?
Go back to working
humiliating part-time jobs?
I wonder if we could make it
on time for that one...
One what?
The Vancouver International
Performance Festival?
That's right.
I did a diabolo exhibition
there the year before last.
It's perfect! If we raise
our international profile,
the Marine Park will
beg to hire us back.
Forget it, the
deadline's already passed.
No!
Wait. If you're talented enough
they'll be willing to skip
the application.
I'll ask the admissions board.
I mean... if you want me to...
Of course we want
you to ask them!
Okay, then.
Rosetta, you're amazing!
I know!
You're a rock star!
I'm so glad that
you're on our side.
Let's get everyone over here
and start practicing!
The inverted Magician.
The enemy's trap.
I say no.
They missed the deadline,
they shouldn't be
allowed to participate.
I can't believe they have
the gall to apply
late to a festival.
But wait. This means they're
not aware that I'm on
the admissions board. I think
we can include them after all.
So you're telling me the
Marine Park owner canceled
their contract because
of something Yuri said?
It seems likely.
I knew you'd want to know what
Freedom Lights is doing next.
I found out they
were accepted into
the Vancouver International
Performance Festival yesterday.
That isn't the festival my
Father's going to be judging,
is it?
Yes. And what's more,
Yuri Killian is a
special advisor for them.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
And I took the liberty
of canceling your flights
to Los Angeles
and San Francisco.
Thank you so much your help.
Don't thank me, you know I'll
do whatever I can to help you.
You're the best.
I hope the rest of
your shoot goes well.
Oh, right. By the
way do you know when
the Vancouver festival is?
Yes, it's this weekend.
This weekend...
If we keep on schedule,
we should be filming your final
fight scenes by next week.
It's funny, you were
my best partner yet.
I don't want to lose this...
There are new developments
at the festival.
Today a new performance group--
they call themselves 'Z'--
was added to the roster.
They're called 'Z'? I think
I've heard of them--
they're an amateur street
performance group, aren't they?
Yes. I hear they're pretty
unusual because amateur teams
usually aren't
allowed to participate.
But what's more strange is that
their show's really similar
to Freedom Lights'.
Cut!
You're a million miles away.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry. Would you
mind if we shot again?
Everyone, take ten.
I called and checked it out
with the festival.
New performers and routines
can be added at any time and
they don't need to be announced.
What is this?
'Z?'
'An acrobatic street performance
team from Vancouver.'
And look at their production--
this is exactly
what ours is like!
Don't tell me
you want to back out.
You probably shouldn't
glare at me like that.
I am pretty influential
at this festival, you know.
Z is an extremely talented
group of amateur performers.
It was my suggestion
that they participate here.
I had to bend a few rules to
make sure they were eligible.
I gather you worry there might
be too many similarities
between your programs.
Well, they are only amateurs.
And you're professionals, right?
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
we're proud to introduce
a troupe from right
here in Vancouver.
Please put your
hands together for Z!
Wow...
The crowd loves them.
Ah, our move...
Hey, we do that in our show!
Are they totally copying us?
They are.
Except they've taken our moves
and made them more dynamic.
Once Freedom Lights performs,
I'll leak to the media that
they stole Z's production.
Then their careers will be over.
It sounds like a good time.
Sure, we'll do it.
And if you do your jobs well,
you will all be welcome
to join me at Kaleido Stage.
Sorry, but I don't
think we're interested.
The audience loves them.
We can't let those guys beat us!
What are we going to do?
Well, if it's an emergency, I
guess we'll have to let you go.
When you come back
for filming next week
I expect you to be perfect.
Ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for Freedom
Lights from Los Angeles!
It can't be!
How dare you show up here
without giving us any notice?
I just wanted to thank you
for the flowers, Yuri.
All right...
Don't you get in my way!
Layla, wait!
Uh, well, how about a round of
applause for Freedom Lights?
Layla Hamilton is no longer
a professional performer,
therefore I'm disqualifying
them from this contest.
Layla.
What are you doing here?
Why aren't you in
London on the film set?
I asked them to
postpone my filming.
You had them do what?
I know you can't
possibly understand this,
but being here was
more important to me.
Why? I thought all this
performing nonsense was
over and done with, Layla.
I'm so sorry. But performing
means so much to me,
and I didn't want to tell you
that because I didn't want you
to be disappointed.
I know I should have told you
the truth earlier, Father.
I just couldn't stand
the thought of letting
my friends down...
Oh, Layla...
Besides I realized something:
I won't be happy acting on
film. I want to be on stage.
At least until until I can
perform the perfect show
I won't be satisfied.
I want to earn the kind of
applause that makes
my whole body tremble!
And for the first time
I have a partner that
can make that happen.
Oh, Layla.
I can't leave this
behind, Father, not yet.
Make sure you get back to
London and finish the filming
as soon as possible.
After that do what you want.
Father! Did you at least
enjoy what I did out there?
You've got to go after him. You
can't leave things like that.
No, Sora. I've been running
after him for too long.
So what now?
What's this?!
This?
Can you see me now, Layla?
But-- that's impossible, there's
no way to do that maneuver.
So now that Layla is able
to see the Fool, that means...
The Legendary Great Maneuver?
But, I always thought
that was just a myth.
And not only that, but Kalos
finally breaks free from
the past and begins
to take action.
Looks like the
Legendary Big Maneuver
is finally in our
grasp. Yeah! Yeah!
Don't miss our next episode,
'The Legendary
Amazing Maneuver.'
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...