[beeps]
[HARUKA pants]
[gasps]
Havin' a good morning, Haruka?
I told you to stop
calling me that.
Yeah, right. I'm sorry, Haru.
Can we go to the entrance
ceremony now?
Why didn't you button this?
You tryin' to look sloppy?
It's tight.
C'mon, it's not that bad.
How did you know where
I was gonna be?
[gasps]
We've been friends so long.
I know everything about you.
Okay, well maybe not everything.
Your mom told me where you were.
Right. Yeah.
So, know what club
you're gonna join, yet?
'Cause I...
Uh?
[clears throat]
So, have you decided
upon a club yet?
Wait, what?
Starting middle school
is a big deal.
I just figured now
would be a good time
to try sounding more
mature, you know?
[HARUKA gasping]
[gasps]
[bird chirps]
[inaudible]
Oh, I see me! I'm in Class Two.
Can you not see it?
I can see for you. Um...
[MAKOTO]
You're in Class One.
Guess we're in
different classes.
Our rooms are right next door.
We'll be together for
joint lessons and P.E.
That's true, but still I--
Hey, Tachibana!
Oh, what's up, Mochizuki?
Just being in Class Two, too!
What? You are, really?
[MOCHIZUKI]
Yeah!
We haven't been in the
same class since what--
third grade, right? [laughs]
[MAKOTO] Uh? Wait!
Where are you goin', Haru?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[ASAHI]
Just think about it, 'kay?
What about you, Numata?
You're gonna join
the swim club, yeah?
No. I hadn't planned on it.
Why? You know you wanna swim.
Who doesn't like fun?
Did you choose a
different club?
You chose a different club!
[NUMATA]
Not yet, but...
Then, what's the problem?
Let's swim together!
[NUMATA]
I don't know, okay.
I was thinking maybe I'd
join the cultural club.
[ASAHI]
You can't be serious.
Isn't that a club for girls?
[KISUMI]
Are you Haruka Nanase?
[gasping]
I'm Kisumi Shigino.
Sano Elementary kid.
And I've actually
heard all about you.
Rin Matsuoka filled me in.
Rin told you?
[KISUMI] Yep. He said there
was this really fast guy
at Iwatobi Swimming Club.
[ASAHI]
Swimming Club?!
Did I hear something
about an SC over here?
[KISUMI]
An "SC"?
It means swimming
club, obviously.
My name's Asahi Shiina.
And you are... Nanase!
Oh yeah, you're definitely
joining the Swim Club. Right?
I haven't decided, yet.
What? You haven't decided?
In that case, come join
the basketball club with me!
[ASAHI] Hey! You can't just
steal him like that.
He's already gonna
join the swim club!
I figure if you already
swim in an outside club,
why join another one?
Might as well try basketball!
[ASAHI]
Shut up!
[BOTH gasp]
[MAKOTO] They put our picture
up. That's kinda cool, huh?
Wonder what Rin's doin' now.
[HARUKA]
Who knows?
Huh?
Haruka! Makoto!
Nagisa, it's not safe
to run out here.
[NAGISA laughs]
Right, sorry.
So, how's middle school going?
Is it awesome?
It's too soon to tell.
We've only been one day.
It's normal.
Yeah?
This isn't fair. I wish I was
in the same year as you guys
so we could all go
to school together.
[MAKOTO] You're only one
year younger than us.
We'll all be back in the same
school soon enough.
Yeah, I know, but that means
I won't be allowed to swim
in the relay with
you two this year.
I don't get to see Rin, either.
Neither do we.
[SASABE]
Haruka! Will you ever
ask permission
before jumping in?!
[HARUKA]
I'm home.
[HARUKA'S MOM]
Welcome back.
Your school seems nice.
How was your class?
[HARUKA]
Fine.
[HARUKA'S MOM laughs]
Was it?
Come down once you've
changed and tell me more.
Dinner's already on the table.
[HARUKA grunts]
[RIN] I'm not going to a
middle school around here.
[RIN]
I'll be in Australia instead.
Yep. I'm gonna be
in the Olympics!
[MAKOTO]
Flying trapeze!
[RAN, REN laugh]
[IKUYA'S MOM]
So, Ikuya.
Do you like your new school?
I can't really tell yet.
[IKUYA'S MOM]
Well, I'm sure you will.
[IKUYA]
Thanks for dinner.
[IKUYA'S MOM]
What? You barely ate!
[IKUYA grunts]
[sighs]
[ASAHI'S SISTER yawns]
Asahi, what exactly
are you doing?
[ASAHI'S SISTER laughing]
[ASAHI]
Stop laughing at me!
[MAKOTO]
I'm heading out!
[doorbell rings]
[HARUKA'S MOM]
Coming!
Good morning, Mrs. Nanase,
how are you?
[HARUKA'S MOM]
Oh, I'm fine, sweetie.
Haruka! Makoto's here!
[HARUKA grunts]
Are you ready to go? Uh!
Yeah, I am if you are.
[sighs]
[STUDENTS chattering]
Nanase! Break for it!
[KISUMI]
I'm open!
[BOTH grunting]
[KISUMI]
Nanase!
[MAKOTO grunts]
[whistle blows]
[MALE TEACHER A]
Okay, that's it!
I need to practice
so I can do that.
You made sucha great shot!
[MAKOTO] Seriously, Haru,
that last shot was incredible.
Thanks, but you still managed to
shut down all of my other ones.
[MAKOTO gasps, laughs]
[ASAHI]
Nanase!
[KISUMI]
Wait for us!
Oh hey, you're that
tall kid from Class Two
who was killing it.
You're uh... Tachibana?
Yep, Makoto Tachibana,
that's me.
It's so nice to meet you.
[ASAHI]
Yeah, yeah, same here!
My name is Asahi Shiina.
[KISUMI] I'm Kisumi Shigino.
Nice to meet you!
All right, be honest
with me, guys.
What'd you think of my rebounds?
Oh, they were cool, I guess.
Well, thank you. To be honest,
I can do pretty much anything
I set my mind to, so...
Which is exactly why you should
join the basketball club.
Not happening.
Nanase and I are
choosing the swim club,
so shut up about it
already. Right?
Wait, you decided to
join the swim club?
I never said what I was joining.
You should if you want, though.
[ASAHI]
What? No way!
Don't tell me you're a member
of the same SC as Nanase?
Uh. I am.
Great, then you can join
the swim club, too!
I what...?!
Aw, come on, don't you wanna
play basketball instead?
Nanase does, don't ya?
I bet you're feeling
popular, Haru.
Haru?
Oh, cuz your first
name's Haruka?
Hey, do you guys mind if I
call you Haru and Makoto?
Someone's desperate
to be accepted.
--I don't care.
--That's fine.
Really?! No fair!
Then I wanna do it, too!
Can I call you Haru and Makoto?!
Can I? Please?
Still don't care.
It's fine.
[gasps] You can both call
me Asahi, if you want.
So, nice to meet you again,
Haru, Makoto, Asahi.
I didn't say you
could call me that!
Don't freak out about it.
You can call me Kisumi, okay?
Oh! He just said "kiss me!"
What a pervy name!
You're the pervy one for even
thinking of it like that.
[laughs] Pervert.
Hey, don't call me that!
I am not a pervert!
[KISUMI]
Okay, fine. Pervert says what?
[ASAHI]
What?
What's up?
[gasps]
[exhales]
[gasps] What's wrong?
New school and everything
making you feel overwhelmed?
I'm good.
It just gets noisy.
Yeah, I bet it does.
There are a lot of
kids in your class
with a whole lot of energy.
Speakin' of which, Kisumi wanted
us to join the basketball club.
Have you decided what
you're gonna do?
[HARUKA]
No. Not yet.
[MAKOTO] You'll have to
make a choice soon.
School rules say we
have to join a club.
Well, have you made a decision?
Me? Let's see... Mm...
No, I don't know, either.
Then, maybe worry
about yourself first.
It's way too hard. There are
just so many to choose from.
You mentioned the
basketball club?
[MAKOTO gasps]
You okay?
[MAKOTO]
Haru.
What if I did join
the basketball club?
Would you be mad?
You don't need my permission
to join the club you want.
That's true, yeah.
So maybe basketball?
I've only ever played it in PE.
But it might be fun to try.
[MAKOTO]
Haru.
What if I did join the
basketball club?
Would you be mad?
[STUDENTS panting]
[KISUMI]
Haru!
We should eat together.
Though, I'll still eat in this
spot even if you say no.
Haru, let's eat lunch together!
Hey, what are you
doing over here?
[KISUMI]
Ooh, fun!
We can all hang out
and eat lunch!
[ASAHI] No we can't! It's just
gonna be me and Haru!
[KISUMI] And me!
Don't get all weird about it.
[KISUMI] Asahi, what elementary
did you graduate from?
I know you didn't go to mine,
or Iwatobi, where Haru went.
Right, that's
because I only just
transferred here back in March.
The elementary I went to
wasn't anywhere close to here.
And let me guess, you were part
of a swimming club there, also?
Yup! At my old SC, I was
known for swimming
the 50 and 100
meter butterfly,
and I always swam
in the medley relay.
Medley relay? What's that?
Don't you know anything?!
Backstroke! Breast!
BF! And Freestyle!
Four people swim a medley of
different strokes in a relay!
Will you please stop trying to
butt into our conversation, now?
I like how even
though you're mad,
you still explained
that really well.
You're a nice guy,
just embrace it.
[ASAHI]
Hm? Yeah, so what.
Like, explaining the obvious
doesn't mean anything, y'know.
[ASAHI sighs] I just wanna
compete at a swim meet,
but if I'm gonna do that,
I'll have to be on a totally
different relay team.
That sorta sucks,
because I'd rather
swim with the guys
from my old SC.
I don't understand why
the both of you
are so obsessed with swimming.
You should give basketball
a chance. For real!
I don't understand
why you're obsessed
with us joining basketball.
I dunno. I guess I just figured
if we joined in
middle school,
we'd be pretty great by the
time we got to high school.
I'm great now.
Did you not watch this?
If I signed up,
I'd be a starter for sure.
Yeah, you're right,
you are awesome.
Why not show everyone?
You just gotta
fill out this form.
[ASAHI]
All right!
Cheater! I'm not joining,
stop asking!
[KISUMI]
Okay, I'm sorry!
[ASAHI] No you're not!
You tried to trick me!
[MAKOTO]
Haru!
[KISUMI] I swear.
I'll stop after you join.
Hey, Makoto, everything okay?
Yeah, just wanted you to
meet this upperclassman.
Very nice to meet you,
Haruka Nanase from Iwatobi SC.
I think you should
join the swim club.
Uh?
[chuckles] He seems to have
strong feelings about it.
I do. Although,
I suppose I have
a pretty valid excuse
to feel that way.
I'm Natsuya Kirishima. I'm
Captain of the swim club, and
I wanted to personally invite
the two of you to join.
Him, too?
Oh, I hope I didn't upset you.
No, you're good.
Haru! Be more respectful!
Sorry.
[laughs] The bottom line is
I want guys you to sign up.
So will you?
Um, so what are you thinking?
Not interested.
Haru!
Have you already decided
what club you're joining?
No, sir. Not yet.
[NATSUYA] We haven't had
a lot of first years join,
so we're in a pinch.
C'mon, please?
Whaddaya think? Should we?
[IKUYA] Does anyone take
the school clubs seriously?
[NATSUYA gasps]
Ikuya. They're not just
fun and games.
[IKUYA] Whatever. You got
tired of competing,
so now you're tryin' to make
new friends in some lame club.
Leave it to my brother
to be that stupid.
You two are brothers, sir?
In fact, we are.
Anyway, I hope you guys think
about joining the club.
We would love to
have you. Ha. Later!
Uh, hey!
[laughs]
He said they don't have
many new members.
I don't know what we should do.
[sighs] Do you know
how gullible you are?
Everyone says that when they're
trying to get people to join.
You think? Really?
[IKUYA] I wouldn't do it
if I were you.
Kirishima, right? So, uh, why
is it you feel that way?
Because students don't
generally take clubs seriously.
For people like us who
compete with an SC,
and don't just like to
pretend we're swimmers,
a stupid school club
would be a waste of time.
I mean, you get that, right?
Not really, but...
...I don't think it's
that big a deal.
How can you think that's
not a big deal?!
[HARUKA gasps]
Whatever.
I just refuse to pretend any
school clubs are serious.
Hey, are you not gonna
finish eating, or what?
There's a lot of "serious"
talk over here.
Oh, you're that weird kid
I catch creepily looking
at me all the time!
What? Shut up, I do not!
Yes, you do.
Guess you wanna be my friend.
That's cool. I mean,
you're not alone.
I'm just a real popular guy!
No.
Couldn't hide it if I wanted to.
Hide what?
All this charisma!
No way! Looking at
you makes me laugh,
like you're an animal
at the zoo.
An animal? What kind?
[IKUYA] Hmph. You remind
me of a monkey.
Would you shut up,
Kisumi, don't laugh!
You're pissing me off.
I'm not a monkey.
If you think I'm a monkey,
then you're a monkey!
No, I'm sorry.
But don't be mad.
Humans come from monkeys,
so it makes perfect sense!
No, it doesn't!
Don't laugh at me!
[IKUYA] See, he's screeching
just like a monkey, isn't he?
Too loud.
[MAKOTO. ASAHI laugh]
Oh! One, two, three, four, five!
[ALL]
Uh?
Who'd have thought it? Go figure
there'd be exactly five of us!
--[ASAHI] I'm not joining!
--[IKUYA] There's no way.
Why won't you let it go?
I don't know.
You haven't decided on a club
yet, so why should I?
I've always been going
with swim club.
I still haven't decided, though.
I don't wanna.
Yeah, me neither.
Huh? Look, I don't
know about this guy,
but Haru and Makoto are
supposed to join swim club!
You're both swimmers, right?!
You gotta choose swim club!
We don't have to do anything.
If we go by your logic,
everyone who can swim
would have to join, right?
Hold on. If you put me in the
"cannot swim" category,
you're wrong again.
What are you mumbling about,
are you saying you can swim?
I've been going to Bando SC
since the first grade.
[KISUMI] Kirishima, you're
a swimmer, too?
That's why I'm not interested
in joining a club
that won't take
swimming seriously.
Oh, come on, how do you know
they won't take it seriously?
[IKUYA] I know they don't split
you into teams based on ability.
I know the practices
are way too easy.
And I know everyone there
would just be screwing around!
[ASAHI]
Hm? Well, I think you're crazy!
You don't know anything!
Yeah, and you
haven't joined yet,
so how can you be
sure I'm wrong?
I can't! I gotta try it first!
[gasps]
[ASAHI] How are you supposed
to find out if you won't do it?
Unless. Maybe you're
just chicken.
[gasps] What did you say?
Face it, you're scared
of jumping into something
you can't be a 100% about.
[NATSUYA]
Dangit.
I forgot to give those guys
a swim club flyer.
Nao would be so mad
if he found out.
[IKUYA] Fine! Then I will
join the stupid club
just to prove to you that
no one takes it seriously!
Hey, there! Sorry to barge in!
[MAKOTO]
Kirishima, sir?
[NATSUYA] I forgot to give
these to you earlier.
Here. You get one.
One for you.
Want a Swim Club Flyer?
No, thanks. I'm going
with basketball.
That's a shame.
He's the only one not
signing up, though, sir.
The rest of us will.
[NATSUYA]
What? Really?
Hey, why am I the only one
that's being left
out of the group?
Just lucky?
What about us?
We didn't agree to join yet.
Haru, you gonna say anything?
It's better than basketball.
You can't decide like that.
Don't knock basketball,
you guys!
You're not gonna back
out now, are you?
No, I'm not backing out!
All right, I'll
see you at the pool
after the Golden Week holidays!
Aw, man, in the end, the
swim club got the rebound
and now has possession
of everyone.
Looks like we wound up
joining a club
without really knowin' what
was going on, didn't we?
[inhales]
[NATSUYA]
Gather round!
[SWIM CLUB]
Yes, sir!
[NATSUYA]
We have new members as of today.
I'm sure you second and third
years already know, but,
soon we're having
a practice swim meet
against Sano Middle School.
An official one will follow.
First years will also be
participating, so stay focused.
[SWIM CLUB]
Yes, sir!
Now. These are our new
first year members.
'Kay, why don't you
introduce yourselves,
starting from the end?
I'm Asahi Shiina, first year.
That's a great intro and all,
but we already know
you're a first year.
[gasps] Guess you're right.
I just moved here last month,
so I'm new to the area.
Uh, I've been part
of an SC before
and am good at the butterfly.
With practice,
I'll get even better.
Nice to meet you all!!
Hey. Ikuya. Go, you're next.
Ikuya Kirishima.
My specialty is breaststroke.
[gasps] Hello, um.
I'm Makoto Tachibana,
I like to swim backstroke.
It's very nice to meet you all.
[applause]
Last is me. Haruka Nanase.
Freestyle only.
Be polite, please.
Thank you.
[applause]
Uh. Now that I think about it,
since you all have
different specialties,
you'll be able to enter
the first-year medley relay.
Individual races for me.
Sir.
And again, I will
only swim freestyle.
[SWIM CLUB]
Uh?
[NATSUYA]
Haruka.
[BOTH gasp]
Don't say my first name.
[NATSUYA] Sorry, what are
you saying to me?
Doesn't matter, as captain, I
won't allow you to just swim
individual races and
only freestyle at that.
Are you refusing
to do the relay?
[HARUKA grunts]
[SWIM CLUB MEMBERS gasp]
Now you listen to me!
Don't get too cocky, kid.
Go on, get in the
pool, right now.
Come on.
We're gonna have
a 50-meter race.
Just for you, freestyle!
You guys, wait!
Our captain won't listen to
anyone after he gets like that.
You might as well give up.
[MAKOTO]
Huh?!
[NATSUYA]
Haruka.
I don't mind you
having convictions,
just earn them by winning.
Don't use my first name.
Are you kidding me, Haru?
This isn't the time for that!
Nao, you can call start.
All right. Take your marks.
Get set.
[whistle blows]
[MALE SWIMMER B]
That kid's fast!
[MALE SWIMMER C]
Like as fast as the captain!
[NATSUYA]
Heh!
[MALE SWIMMER D]
Here's the turn!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
The captain can't shake him!
[ASAHI gasping]
[MALE SWIMMER C]
Whoa! They're neck and neck!
[panting]
That was impressive. You tied.
We did?
Damn it.
[panting]
All right, you really
are fast, first year.
You proved it, and I'll let
you swim just freestyle.
It was only a tie, however.
So you'll still swim relay.
The next time we race,
it won't be a tie.
Haru...
Now, you all ready
to start practice?
[SWIM CLUB]
Yes, sir!
[IKUYA]
You're really fast.
I'm just normal.
No, that was fast!
Like, I still can't believe it!
[NATSUYA] Hey, guys!
First years are over here!
[FIRST YEARS]
Yes, sir!
This is Nao Serizawa,
a third year member as well
as our club manager.
He's also in charge of
teaching the first years.
You're lucky to learn from him.
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
And you are...
...Asahi, Ikuya,
Makoto, and Haruka.
First name again.
You really hate being called
by your first name that much?
Well, you're gonna have
to deal with it!
All club members call each
other by first name here.
That's our motto!
[BOTH gasp, groan]
[NAO] Listen, because swimmers
usually compete as individuals,
it can be easy to
get self-centered.
But that won't work
in a club like ours.
This way, we can
form better bonds.
All right, Nao, get to it.
Well, then. I've been
entrusted with teaching you
guys and making
sure you get better.
But I think I'll start things
off by showing you around.
[inaudible]
[NAO]
Great! Let's end things today
with a simple 200
meter freestyle.
Keep in mind, this will be
part of your cool down,
so don't feel like you
need to go all out.
Yes, sir.
Okay, who's next?
And the next.
--And the last.
--Yes, sir.
[gasps]
[MAKOTO gasps]
Come on, Asahi,
don't mess around.
[laughs] Sorry.
[gasps]
[HARUKA]
What's wrong?
Uh. I, uh.
[MAKOTO]
Asahi?
I hope this isn't
some stupid joke.
No. It's not.
I can't swim freestyle anymore!
[BOTH gasp]
What?
[NATSUYA] Huh. So you suddenly
couldn't swim anymore?
[ASAHI]
Right.
[IKUYA] You sure it's not that
you just can't swim freestyle?
No, that's not it!
That's not it at all!
I, uh, I could, but then
I couldn't do it. [groaning]
But why now, out of nowhere?
How should I know?
[NAO]
Hm... Well, maybe it's mental.
Mental?
It's cool. Don't worry.
If you were able to
swim it before,
then you'll be able
to swim it again.
Yeah!
[gasping]
[NATSUYA]
Ikuya!
Don't worry, you're a lot better
than you were earlier.
I'm really proud of you!
I promise you're gonna
get the hang of it, soon.
Just keep at, 'kay? [laughs]
Big brother.
Hey, Ikuya, what's wrong?
Wait!
Whoa, what's the deal with him?
[MAKOTO]
I wonder if Asahi will be okay.
[HARUKA]
Who knows?
[MAKOTO]
Natsuya and Ikuya are brothers,
but they sure don't
seem to get along.
[HARUKA]
Who knows?
[MAKOTO] Ah, you're not
even listening to me.
Hey, lookie!
Haru and Mako are here.
You guys are late!
Yeah, that's because Haru and I
joined our school's swim club.
You have a swim club?
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, everyone at school's
required to join something, so.
[NAGISA]
Mm...
Uh. We still plan to come here
though, if that's cool?
[gasps] Of course! You should!
Oh, that reminds me! Coach said
that I could try something new.
Meaning, at the next meet,
I'm gonna get to swim
in the 50 meter and the 100
meter breaststroke races!
No way. That's awesome, Nagisa!
[NAGISA] What do you think
you two will do?
[MAKOTO] Mm... Well,
there's supposed to be
a couple of meets with the
swim club coming up soon.
I should probably
prioritize those.
[NAGISA]
Really? What about Haru?
I guess I'll stick with Makoto.
I see.
I'll go, though. To cheer.
[MAKOTO]
Mm-hm.
We couldn't miss out on
your spectacular swimming.
You'll go? Nice!
Then I'm gonna go practice!
[SASABE] Nagisa! I told you
not to run by the pool!
[NAGISA]
Whoops! Sorry, Coach!
[ASAHI]
Mental.
Ugh. Why are there so many?!
I have no idea which one
of these I should get!
[REI] Please keep it down,
this is a library.
[gasps] I'm sorry.
Hey, do you like books, kid?!
Really. I am not
with this loud boy.
Why ask me that, and why can't
you be quiet when asking?
Sorry, you're wearing glasses,
so I figured you
liked reading stuff.
You're jumping to conclusions.
Uh? Come on.
You gotta help me!
Listen, I'm desperate to find
the right book and leave,
but I don't know which
one I should choose!
[sighs] All right, what kind of
book are you trying to find?
If helping will give me peace
and quiet, then I'll help you.
[ASAHI]
Thanks!
Okay, my goal is to
be good at swimming,
so I need a book
to help me do that!
If there's a book like that,
then I want it, too.
Huh? Say what?
[REI]
Nothing, never mind.
Anyway, that is hardly
a good explanation.
I'm going to need to hear
some more details.
[ASAHI]
Oh, sure.
So, uh, I could swim
freestyle until yesterday.
And then... I randomly
couldn't do it.
I didn't realize that
was even possible.
It's possible!
I'm telling you it happened,
and I don't lie!
Really? That it so bizarre,
but it's conceivable.
His mental state could be
affecting his body somehow.
Hey, what are you
muttering about?
Do you want me to help you,
or don't you?
[ASAHI]
Uh!
[REI] I believe you should
begin by reading these.
Whoa! Thank you!
[laughs]
I'm certain mental training
books are a great supplement,
but you might need to admit
some stuff to yourself
to get to the root
of this problem.
You're a real lifesaver!
Thanks a lot!
Hey! I was not done
speaking with you!
[alarm blares]
[ASAHI]
Wait, what?
Is that me?
[BOOK CLERK A]
Hey, kid!
You can't just leave without
checking those out!
Check what out?
Let go! Uh. Hey! Hold on!
[ASAHI]
I am a genius.
I am a genius. I am a genius.
I am a genius. I am
a genius. I am a genius.
I am a genius.
I am a genius. I am a
genius. I am a genius.
I'm a genius. I am a genius!
A genius!
[ASAHI'S SISTER]
Knock it off, will you!
[KISUMI] Well, basketball
club practice is tough.
How's the swim club going?
[HARUKA]
Normal.
That's your answer
for everything, Haru.
[KISUMI]
Hey. Kirishima.
[IKUYA]
Uh! Yeah. What is it?
You can join us for
lunch, if you want.
[IKUYA]
Mm. I um, no thanks
What do you want?
Uh! Nothin'.
For real, you can sit here!
Come on, do it.
I wanna talk to you, too!
Fine. I guess I don't
have a choice, now.
I wouldn't want to be rude.
[ASAHI]
♪ Lunch time! Lunch time! ♪
Hey!
What made you decide you
could sit over here?!
[ASAHI] I can sit wherever
I want, that a problem?
No, but that's the seat
where I was planning to sit!
No problem, you can
sit on my lap!
[ASAHI] Have you lost it?!
I'm not gonna sit there!
You are the funniest person!
Man, this sucks.
[KISUMI]
Asahi, you can try to be a jerk,
but we all know
you're a good guy.
[ASAHI]
Oh, shut up.
Did the thing from
yesterday get better?
Yeah, that? Meh, I dunno.
What thing from yesterday?
[IKUYA]
No big deal.
He just forgot how to swim.
Just freestyle! Freestyle!
How's that possible?
[ASAHI]
I dunno, it just is!
But I borrowed books on
mental training yesterday,
so I can fix it. [chuckles]
I'll be back to normal
in no time!
Uh. At least I hope I will be.
Hm... Truth is, I'm at a loss.
[KISUMI]
Why's that?
Because, well...
Okay, see, step one of the first
phase says I'm supposed to find
all of my weaknesses,
but that's been a challenge.
Yeah. I'm pretty much perfect.
I have like zero weaknesses.
[laughs] Zero!
If you ask me, your main
weakness is that you're stupid.
Very stupid.
And there's no cure for
being stupid! [laughs]
I swear, I'll beat
the crap out of you guys!
Yeah, you know, this is exactly
what's so great about you!
Oh, shut up!
Ha!
So, anyway one book I
read said that I needed
to start talking about myself
with more positivity.
Yep. Self-suggestion works,
and that's why I've been staring
in the mirror and saying
"I am a genius" over and
over and over again!
[KISUMI] And you feel like
that's actual training?
Yeah, isn't it?
You're so stupid.
[ASAHI]
Stop saying that!
I'm just following
the directions!
[KISUMI]
I'm sure it'll be fine.
[ASAHI]
I know!
[KISUMI] Right? Perspective
is everything,
even if it is simple.
[ASAHI]
Yes, thank you!
What is it?
What's what?
--[gasping]
--[HARUKA slurping]
[slurping]
[gasps, coughs]
[panting]
What is going on with you guys?
I have no idea. Ask him.
What? Nothing!
Stop copying me.
[IKUYA]
Stop copying you?!
[laughs]
Ikuya, you're pretty
hilarious, too!
Don't you dare lump
me in with him!
What do you mean by that?!
Exactly what I just said!
And I don't remember
saying that you could
call me by my first name!
[MOCHIZUKI]
Tachibana, make sure you wait!
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, that's what I'm doin'.
[KISUMI laughing]
Tell me these guys are
cracking you up, Haru!
They're not.
[IKUYA] I don't think
it's that funny, either!
[ASAHI] I go out of my way
to eat lunch with you all,
and this is how I get treated?
Maybe you should
eat somewhere else!
[IKUYA] No, maybe you should
[ASAHI]
Why would I do that?!
I'm not the weird one
who's only over here
because I wanna copy Haru!
Don't jump on me like that.
[IKUYA]
I wasn't copying him!
We just happened to be
eating the same way.
[KISUMI]
Something wrong, Haru?
No, it's nothing.
[MALE TEACHER B]
Attention.
What boy's on duty
for Class One?
It says Nanase on the board.
[HARUKA grunts]
[FEMALE STUDENT C] Do you
think he meant it, though?
[FEMALE STUDENT D]
I mean, obviously.
[FEMALE STUDENT C]
Oh, I hope you're right.
That was a close one, huh?
[NATSUYA]
So, how's club going?
[HARUKA]
Normal. Sir.
[NATSUYA]
I'm glad to hear that.
I don't know what
I would've done
if you said you wanted
to quit already.
Has Ikuya said anything about
maybe wanting to quit?
[HARUKA]
Not to me.
But you might want to ask him
about that yourself, sir.
You're not very good
at the whole being polite
thing, are you?
You should work on that.
[sighs]
[HARUKA] Why don't you
and Ikuya get along, sir?
I can only guess,
but it's most likely because
I pushed him away.
That would fit with the
timeline of him completely
hating my guts for
the past two years.
I doubt he really hates you.
[NATSUYA]
Uh?
Hope you're right.
[NATSUYA]
Here.
Let me know if you feel like
this is too much to carry.
Look, I realize my brother's
got some issues.
Just gotta be patient, yeah?
Welp, see you at practice.
Um.
I really appreciate
your help, sir.
[gasps]
Sure. It's no problem.
[ASAHI]
Hm?
Uh, Ikuya, what's going on?
With what?
You're copying--
No, I am not!
Yeah, so. What's
that guy's deal?
Uh.
How's it goin', first years?
[MAKOTO]
Oh, hello, sir.
It's going well!
[ASAHI]
It's good, sir!
--[HARUKA] Normal.
--Great.
No words from Ikuya?
Normal.
How you feeling, Asahi?
Think you can swim freestyle?
You bet!
Nao said that it might
be a mental issue,
so I borrowed some books from
the library to help out.
They specifically deal with
mental training stuff,
and I think they're already
making a difference.
Yeah? Nice work!
[ASAHI laughs]
[NATSUYA]
I'm hopin' for the best!
[ASAHI] Thank you, sir.
I'm pretty sure I'll be fine!
Well, I'm leavin'
these guys to you.
[MALE SWIMMER D]
Captain, you ready to go?
[NATSUYA]
Yep! Be right there!
Funny. He really is awkward.
So, you guys ready to swim?
[FIRST YEARS]
Yes, sir!
[IKUYA]
[NAO]
We'll practice starting first.
Let's try the track start.
One foot forward
and one foot back.
Don't bend your knees too much!
And watch that reaction time!
Ready!
[whistle blows]
[NAO]
Next!
Ready!
[whistle blows]
[whistle blowing]
Uh.
[NAO]
It's not good.
There's too much time
between the sound
of the whistle and
when you jump.
Gotta take advantage of that
start, or you'll never win.
I want you to crouch with
your focus under your belly
button, around here.
Everyone try.
That's where your body's
center is located.
So, it should help you
feel more stable.
That's physically and mentally.
Take a deep breath while
you're in that position,
and let it all out at once.
When you let go, try to exhale
all of your tension as well.
[exhaling]
This next part's important.
After you let that air out,
I want you to take
shallow breaths,
and imagine your body is ears.
Ear ears?
Yup. For real.
All the nerves in your body
are listening for that whistle.
This is not easy.
Ears, huh?
Yeah, it's hard to understand.
But that's okay.
Uh. It's okay?
Yep, in the end, you just have
to remember how it feels to you.
All right, guys,
that's good. Follow me.
Let's play a speed game
[ASAHI, IKUYA, MAKOTO]
Uh...?
[MAKOTO] Um, Nao.
What are we doing?
I told you, it's a speed game.
Put both hands on the mat.
Lift your hips a bit.
Then, whoever grabs or
swipes this cap first wins.
If you keep practicing,
you'll get a feel
for what it means to turn
your whole body into ears.
Ah.
[NAO]
We can start with Haruka.
Makoto, you blow the whistle.
Yes, sir.
[MAKOTO]
Uh...
I'm not too shabby, am I?
[laughs] Looks like Haru's
the slowest of us all!
I'll go next and win for sure.
[whistle blows]
[ASAHI gasping]
[IKUYA]
Uh!
[whistle blows]
[MAKOTO gasping]
You monster.
What? I didn't say anything.
Why is he a manager?
He's amazing.
Okay, listen up.
Next, we need to work
on the relay exchange.
We don't have much time
before our practice meet
with Sano Middle School.
[MAKOTO]
Haru, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Let's do this guys.
Move, hop in.
Get on your mark.
Get set...
[whistle blows]
Too fast, Ikuya!
That was a false start!
[panting]
[gasps]
Too slow!
You've gotta take less
time than a flat start!
That was slow, too!
Haru...
His swimming's gotten sloppy.
But he swam fine yesterday.
[NAO]
Interesting.
Why's he falling apart now?
Think he's scared of the relay?
Is he?
Maybe.
We won the medley
in elementary though.
What reason would he
have to be scared?
We were so good.
Best relay team ever.
I bet he's just havin' a hard
timing believing there could be
a better team than the one
we were already on, sir.
That makes sense.
You're okay, though, right?
I'm sad as well, I guess.
But at least we're
both still swimming!
[NAO] True. And why do you
swim, do you like it?
[gasps] Yes.
[NAO]
Really?
You're not just here
because Haruka is?
[MAKOTO gasps]
[NAO]
Relax.
I'm sorry, that was
a mean question.
[inhales] Okay.
Go! You're almost there!
[panting]
[ASAHI]
Haru! Good for you!
[panting]
Oh, yeah. Good job!
Really good.
[panting]
[NAO] You'll be able to
reduce your time a lot
if you improve your exchanges.
But right now,
I'm fairly certain
your mindset keeps you focused
on being individuals.
That's gonna be it for today!
Join the rest of the team
to say bye, okay?
--[ASAHI] Okay.
--[HARUKA] Okay.
[gasps] Okay.
[ASAHI]
Eh, we'll work it out.
Yeah, I'm actually
not all that worried.
Who cares if we're
good at exchanges?
As long as our individual
times stay fast,
it won't be a problem.
[HARUKA]
Makoto.
Oh, sorry. I zoned out.
What's up?
Did something like, happen?
What? No, nothing happened.
[ASAHI]
I think something did.
I think you got worried
about the relay.
Oh, yeah. I mean, I am worried.
[ASAHI]
I said it'll be fine.
We've got plenty of time
before even the practice meet.
That's true.
[ASAHI]
Well. Ikuya and I are this way.
How in the world did we end
up walking home together?
Obviously, that's because we
live in the same direction.
[IKUYA]
Stupid Asahi.
[ASAHI]
What did you say? I'm not wrong.
We do live in the
same direction.
[HARUKA]
Makoto.
[MAKOTO]
Yeah?
Something happened, right?
I don't really know
what you mean.
Why are you lying?!
[gasps]
It's the truth though.
Huh? Are, you sure?
[MAKOTO]
I'm sure. It's nothing.
Anyway, I'll see you tomorrow.
I'm home.
[HARUKA'S MOM]
Oh, Haruka, welcome back.
Listen, I got a call from
your dad's company today.
They told me he had been
injured while he was working.
He was?
[HARUKA'S MOM] Oh, don't worry.
He's fine, it's not bad.
It's just gonna be difficult
for him to get around
out here until
he heals back up.
So, I think he'll need
me to go help him.
How long will you be gone?
[HARUKA'S MOM] Mm... I think
about a week, starting tomorrow?
What do you want to do?
I know you have
school to consider.
I'll be fine by myself
if it's not too long.
[HARUKA'S MOM] You sure?
I'm gonna be so worried.
I can ask the Tachibanas to
keep an eye on you, though!
[NAO] Really? You're not just
here because Haruka is?
[MAKOTO]
That's not it.
[MAKOTO'S MOM] Hey, Haruka,
how's your morning going?
Did Makoto not tell
you he left early?
He said he had to do
his class duties.
[gasps]
Oh, your mom's leaving today to
go be with your dad, isn't she?
Come over for dinner
starting tonight, okay?
[HARUKA]
Yes, ma'am. Thank you.
[MAKOTO panting]
[gasps]
[SASABE]
Hey, Makoto!
Don't you have class duty today?
[MAKOTO]
Yeah!
[SASABE]
What's wrong?
Swimming so early in the
morning isn't really like you.
Yes, it is. I do love
swimming, you know.
Huh?
[MAKOTO]
Well, I'm off to school.
Yeah, right.
That was weird. Real weird.
[ASAHI]
Hey, Haru.
Is that all you're
eating for lunch?
Grilled mackerel.
Seems bland compared
to yesterday.
My parents won't be
home for a while.
[ASAHI]
What?
How long are they
gonna be away for?
Only like a week.
Whoa! And you'll be
alone that entire time?
It's not really that big a deal.
It's not? There's no way
I'd ever survive that.
[ASAHI]
Yeah, same here. I...
Haru will be fine
alone, just fine.
[ASAHI] ...I would die of
starvation in three days!
[KISUMI]
Yeah, I'm not sure you would die
even if you were killed, Asahi.
[ASAHI]
Huh? Is that a compliment?
[HARUKA]
It's burnt...
[NAO] The next five will be
intervals of 50-meter freestyle.
Asahi, are you okay?
[ASAHI]
Oh, yes, sir!
[NAO] I'll be timing you, too.
Haruka's up first.
[whistle blows]
Next, Asahi.
[gasps] Right!
[whistle blows]
[gasps]
[ASAHI panting]
Damn.
It's all right, Asahi,
don't push yourself!
[yells]
[NAO]
Makoto's next.
--[MAKOTO] Ready!
--[whistle blows]
[ASAHI]
Haru.
Would you mind sharing with
me how you swim freestyle?
I thrust my fingers into
the water's surface
without fighting against
it to make a cut.
Then, I slide my body in after.
What does that even mean?!
[exhales] I used to be able to.
[NAO]
Individual specialties next.
I want five 100-meter intervals,
one every three minutes,
and they'll be timed.
Ya wanna race?
[whistle blows]
[NAO]
What a surprise.
Who won this time?!
[NAO]
Natsuya by a hair.
[NATSUYA grunts]
[gasps]
[MAKOTO panting]
Makoto?
You good?
You swam more than
the 10 lengths, yeah?
[MAKOTO]
Yeah. I did an extra one.
You're not gonna help
yourself get any better
if you swim recklessly.
No, I'll be all right.
I just need to rest
for a little bit.
Then...
...I can go again.
Your thoughts?
Their individual
times aren't bad.
Their problem will be
slow relay exchanges.
We'll be practicing
the relay from now on.
[ASAHI, MAKOTO]
Right!
[NATSUYA growls]
Ready...
[whistle blows]
Too slow, don't be so careful.
[NAO]
Too fast, be more careful!
Are you trying to go slow?
Not good, guys.
You're slow. Why do you
think that is?
Exchanges, probably?
Exchanges.
Can anyone tell me
why they're so bad?
Do you want to swim the relay?
[ALL grunt]
We can just swim
individual races.
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH grunt]
Like I said, I'm fine
with individual freestyle.
Haru.
Too bad. Like I said,
they can't swim the
relay without you!
Well, they all want to
race individually, too.
Yeah, he's right. And besides,
there's no way we'll win
a relay with this team.
Hey, you don't speak for me!
I wanna do the relay,
and I think we can win!
Fine, then why don't you
start by doing your part?!
Asahi, your swimming is
way too self-centered.
What?! You shut up!
Stop it! Your exchanges
aren't going very well
because you all swim selfishly
and only ever think
about yourselves.
Relays are different!
Grow up! Think beyond
your own needs!
All of you, take a break
and go cool off!
[ALL exhale]
[NAO]
Asahi!
[ASAHI]
Hey, Nao.
[NAO]
Hey. So, you all right?
I know Natsuya was
pretty harsh on you guys.
No. He was just telling
the truth, sir.
And, you know...
The more I think about
what Ikuya told me, the uh,
the more he seems right about
me being selfish when I swim.
I don't know how to fix it.
Ah...
[ASAHI]
I just...
How do I even focus
on the relay?
I'm scared.
Scared? Why's that?
Because, sir. What if...
What if...
What if I forget about
the other strokes, too?!
What then?
[gasps]
[cries]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[HARUKA]
Makoto.
Yeah, um, what is it?
[HARUKA]
You know you were practicing
recklessly today, right?
[MAKOTO]
I don't think that's true.
[HARUKA] Then why go faster
and farther than normal?
[MAKOTO] Because,
we have a meet coming up.
I mean. It's also because
I like swimming.
Huh? Uh. Where did
that come from?
[gasps] Haru, don't you think
that's a little rude to ask?
But to answer you. Well,
obviously it came from me
wanting to swim more
because I like doing it.
--So, today.
Oh, sorry. You go first.
What is it?
No, you should go first.
So today, when you
said it was fine
to just be in individual races,
what was that about?
[HARUKA] Nothing.
I just said what I thought.
I've never really liked relays.
[MAKOTO] You didn't
mind swimming them
in elementary school.
Things changed, and I don't feel
like swimming them anymore.
It's really not that
complicated.
Yeah, I suppose it is
different without Rin around.
He'd convince you.
[HARUKA] Don't talk about
people who aren't here.
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, right. Sorry.
Okay, what were you
about to say earlier?
Why did you leave
without me this morning?
[MAKOTO gasps]
Oh, I had class duty. Sorry, uh.
I must've just forgotten
to tell you.
But, you've never forgotten
to tell me before now.
Maybe I haven't, but,
I don't know, I...
Getting used to all this
new stuff is really hard!
I mean, you just said things
have changed for you, right?!
Well, things can be
different for me, too!
That's true.
[MAKOTO] You're still gonna
come over for dinner, yeah?
I think I'll eat
at home, thanks.
Huh. I thought your mom
had already left, though.
I can figure something out.
Thank you for this meal.
[ASAHI]
I am a genius.
I am a genius. I am a genius.
I am... a... gen... ius.
[NATSUYA sighs]
[IKUYA]
Why not change up our training?
What do you mean change up?
Just that, we don't need
to practice exchanges.
If we all swim our personal
best, then we'll be fine.
[NATSUYA] That attitude is
why you have a hard time
keeping pace with
the other guys.
Are you tryin' to say
it's all my fault?!
And everyone else
agrees with you?
Bet they do! Don't they?!
Don't talk about your friends
that way when you're the one
who refuses to see
your own failings.
A relay requires a team.
A team, huh? And friends?
Funny story. Especially coming
from you of all people.
It's easy to tell me to
expand my horizons,
make new friends, when you...
You never even wanted to
be my friend, right?!
Well, if you don't,
then why would they?!
Ikuya!
[IKUYA cries]
[NAO]
Captain skipping practice?
Not a good look.
[NATSUYA]
Leave me alone.
[NAO] Why don't you stop
pushing him away?
Or do you like being
this depressed?
[NATSUYA]
How did you even know?
Easy. You don't really get
depressed about too much else.
[NATSUYA]
Whatever. I have to do it.
If I don't, then he won't
ever become independent.
[NATSUYA]
How's Asahi?
[NAO]
He's scared.
But I think he'll be fine.
He's got a strong spirit and
wants to improve himself.
[NATSUYA]
Gotcha.
I bet he'll make a
great captain one day.
Makoto?
[NAO]
He's wavering.
But he's working
through some stuff.
He'll get stronger soon.
[NATSUYA]
Haruka?
[NAO]
Kid's a prodigy.
It's not often you see
such a clean streamline.
When it comes to the relay,
though, he starts falling apart.
[NATSUYA] I wish he
would pay more attention
to his surroundings.
Same as Ikuya, isn't he?
[NATSUYA]
Ikuya.
[NAO] He swims in a way
that minimizes fatigue.
That's why he can swim long
distances without dropping pace.
[NATSUYA] My little brother's
pretty amazing, huh?
And he'll get faster. Trust me.
[NATSUYA]
Don't let me down.
[MALE ADVISOR A]
All right. Let the practice meet
between Sano and Iwatobi
Middle Schools begin!
[SWIMMERS]
Have a good swim meet!
[SOSUKE]
Nanase. Tachibana.
[BOTH gasp]
Hello.
I'm Sosuke Yamazaki,
and I'm from Sano SC.
Sano SC? That's where Rin went.
That's right. Hey, let's see
who's faster at freestyle.
[HARUKA grunts]
See ya.
[MAKOTO grunts]
[MALE ADVISOR A]
Ready...
--[whistle blows]
--[SWIM CLUB cheering]
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Makoto!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Makoto!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Iwatobi!
[panting]
[MALE SWIMMER B] Let's go, let's
go, let's go, let's go, Ikuya!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Ikuya!
Iwatobi!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Asahi!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Asahi!
Iwatobi!
[ASAHI grunts]
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Let's go! Let's go,
let's go, let's go,
let's go, Haruka!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Haruka!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Push it! Push it,
push it, push it,
push it, Haruka!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Push it! Push it, push it,
push it, push it, Haruka!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Haruka!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Haruka!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Push it! Push it, push it,
push it, push it, Haruka!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Iwatobi!
[SOSUKE]
Nanase!
You underestimating me?!
Calm down, Sosuke.
[SOSUKE grunts]
Whatever.
[panting]
[whistle blowing]
[MALE ADVISOR A]
Ready...
--[whistle blows]
--[IWATOBI SWIMMERS] Go!
[SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, Makoto!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Push it! Push it,
push it, push it, Makoto!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Push it! Push it,
push it, push it, Makoto!
They're not even trying.
[SANO SWIMMER B]
Go!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Ikuya!
[gasps] Damn!
Too slow.
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go,
let's go, let's go,
let's go, Asahi!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Asahi!
Why's he so slow?
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Let's go! Let's go,
let's go, let's go,
let's go, Haruka!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Haruka!
Iwatobi!
[panting]
Here.
[panting] I'm fine.
[NATSUYA]
Nice work, everyone.
Get some rest today.
We'll get right back
to it tomorrow.
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Right!
You're all dismissed!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Thank you, Captain!
[NATSUYA]
First years.
How'd you feel about the relay?
[ALL exhale]
Get used to losing if
you keep up this mess.
I'm just being honest.
Sano functions together
much better as a team.
He's right. You can't win
if you don't change.
Teamwork, you guys.
Focus on it now.
Believe me, individually,
you'll all do better, too.
[ALL gasp]
[SOSUKE]
Hey! Haruka Nanase!
[MAKOTO]
Yamazaki.
What was that swimming about?
You too good for me?
Actually, my swimming has
nothing to do with you.
Don't mess with me!
Don't mess with us!
Stop.
But this guy--
I said stop.
[ASAHI growls]
Look, have you thought about how
Rin must feel when he swims now?
What he's going through?
Rin?
Do you think he would be
satisfied with that swim?
Do you?!
Yeah, satisfying Rin is not
the reason I swim, sorry!
[SOSUKE growls]
[MAKOTO] Come on, you guys.
Calm down, okay?
Remember this. Rin wanted
to swim with you
because he thought
you were great.
If you can't be bothered
to try without him here,
then don't waste our time!
[gasps] A letter from Rin.
[gasps] No kidding?
[SOSUKE]
Hmph.
You won't read it?
No, I won't.
[RIN]
I'm officially going in April.
Really? Leaving for
Australia, at last?
Yep.
I know your dad would
be proud of you,
aiming for the
world like he did.
Not the world.
It's more like I feel if I jump
into somewhere foreign,
I'll be forced to figure
the rest out.
Sounds like you.
But. I'll go to
Iwatobi before that.
Uh. To Iwatobi? What for?
Because, well. I wanna
swim with a kid
at that school who I bet
would own the relay.
[SOSUKE]
Uh.
Iwatobi.
Nanase swims freestyle,
so you'll do butterfly?
Oh, I guess so, yeah.
Wait, you swim butterfly,
don't you?
Of course I do.
I swim it better than you.
[RIN] Why say that?!
Trying to piss me off?
[SOSUKE growls]
[MAKOTO] Haru, you should come
over for dinner tonight.
[HARUKA]
No. I'll eat at home.
Dinner's ready.
[IKUYA]
Not hungry!
[ASAHI]
I'm a genius.
I'm a genius. I'm a genius.
[sighs]
Am I...?
Am I really a genius?
[panting]
[doorbell chimes]
[HARUKA, MAKOTO gasp]
Haru. Uh.
Is that your dinner?
[gasps] What I eat
isn't your business.
Oh, yes it is my business!
Hey. You haven't been
eating any of the food
I've brought over, have you?
No wonder you were slow today!
I get that you don't want to eat
with me, and that's fine,
but don't tell me you'll
figure something out
if you're not gonna
actually figure--
Let go!
[gasps]
I'm not the only
selfish one here.
What would you call the
way you've been acting?
You changed out of nowhere!
Meanwhile, you tell me
nothing's going on.
[gasps]
I don't understand
what this is about.
What happened?
Why try to be something
you're not?
Haru...
Makoto, be Makoto!
[gasps]
I should be myself.
You should.
[MAKOTO]
Haru! Come with me, right now!
Let's go, hurry!
[HARUKA]
Hey!
[sighs]
This is nice.
[MAKOTO]
It's funny.
I thought I'd be different once
I started middle school.
I thought that I
wanted to change,
then I started freakin' out.
It was like I suddenly
had no choice anymore.
Nao didn't help, either.
He asked me one day if I
actually liked swimming.
He wanted to know
if the only reason
I was in swim club
was because of you.
Really?
So, once I started
thinking about it,
it kinda messed with me.
I couldn't tell if I
still liked swimming.
Maybe I was only there because
I wanted to be with you.
Is that why you
kept avoiding me?
I wasn't avoiding you,
not on purpose.
I dunno, it's just
that I wasn't sure
I could figure it out
if you were there, too.
It was confusing.
To you, though, it seemed
like I didn't want you around.
I did. Sorry.
No big deal.
Guess, I was wrong, too.
[HARUKA] So, then,
did you find your answer?
[MAKOTO]
I think it's both.
[HARUKA]
"Both"?
[MAKOTO] Mm-hm. I didn't
know how I felt for a while,
so I wound up trying too hard.
But I think I can start
having fun again now.
Even just swimming around
like this feels good.
Being in the water
really helps out.
I feel better about everything.
The truth is...
I really do like to swim.
But I realized. I want
you to be there, too.
[gasps]
I do.
I love swimming,
and I love Haruka,
so, let's swim together!
[gasping]
[MAKOTO laughs]
Stop saying my
whole first name.
Right. Haru.
Yes.
Also, um.
[MAKOTO]
Hm?
Don't be silly, of course
I'll swim with you.
[HARUKA]
We should probably go home.
[MAKOTO laughs]
Well, wait for me!
[gasping]
[MAKOTO]
Nao, sir.
[NAO]
What's up?
What did you want to tell me?
[MAKOTO]
Just that.
Yes, I like how Haru swims.
And I can't deny swimming
because Haru was there.
Except, when we lost the relay,
it really bothered me.
[MAKOTO]
I like it. I like swimming.
That's why...
Why I'm ready to
do what it takes.
I wanna win the relay!
Got it.
I just needed to say that.
I have a feeling you'll
win the next one.
Thanks!
[clock chimes]
[MAKOTO] Hey guys.
You ready for practice?
Makoto?
What are you doing here?
You don't normally
come in our class.
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, I just felt like it.
[ASAHI]
Mm? Fine with me.
Hey, Ikuya, we're
gonna go practice!
[IKUYA]
I'm not goin'.
Ikuya?
Why are you being so stupid?
We need to practice, bad!
How else will we get
revenge on Sano?
[IKUYA]
Not my problem.
I'm quitting the swim club.
[gasps] What are you
even talking about?!
Stop screwing around!
[MAKOTO]
What happened?
Listen, your joke?! It sucks!
Back off! This isn't some joke!
Hey! Ikuya, wait!
Guys, hold up, please!
Come with me, right now.
Again...?
[IKUYA panting]
[ASAHI]
Don't do it! Ikuya, no!
[IKUYA grunting]
[IKUYA]
Ow, that hurts!
What do you think you're
doing, you idiot?!
C'mon, you can't kill yourself
just because you lost one time!
No! That's not it!
You're the idiot.
I wasn't gonna kill myself.
You're such a weirdo.
Get off, jeez.
[panting]
[IKUYA] What is this?
Why did you all follow me?
Why do you think we followed
you, we're worried!
[gasps]
About what?
About you.
After all, we're a team.
[gasps]
Hold on. You were heading
to that swim club, huh?
It's the one where my brother
and I were members.
We always said we'd compete
internationally together.
We worked hard, too.
But the second he
started middle school,
something changed.
He pushed me away.
When I asked him why,
he just told me
to expand my horizons and
make new friends.
I'm so angry and I
can't forgive him.
What kind of person treats
his own brother that way?
I don't think he
meant to be mean.
Sounds to me as if he wanted
you to be more independent
so you could do all that
stuff on your own.
You know what else.
I bet he misses you.
As a big brother, I get it.
I talked to Natsuya a bit, and
he's just worried about you.
It really bothers him
that you hate him.
Sounded lonely to me.
It's okay. Big brothers
and little brothers
don't have to get along
every second, right?
But now, you don't
have to be alone.
[IKUYA] I always thought
things would be fine
as long as he was there.
I didn't need anyone else.
Like, I didn't need teammates,
and I didn't need any
friends that weren't him.
When he left,
I decided to stay with the club,
but I swam by myself.
[IKUYA cries]
It was awful.
I was so lonely.
You were lonely.
[IKUYA] I thought if
I could be like Haru,
then maybe my brother would
pay attention to me again.
[MAKOTO] Oh, so that's why
you were copying him.
[ASAHI]
And you call me stupid.
You're fast enough without
having to do stuff like that.
And, trust me,
I'm sure Natsuya knows.
How could he not?
Right? Haru?
Was I...
Was I lonely, too?
Huh? Say what?
Ikuya.
You're not me, and that's okay.
You don't belong in my shadow,
or in Natsuya's either.
So, line up next
to the rest of us.
[cries]
Uh! Uh! Wait. I think
I have a towel.
Crap! Here!
Use this!
Huh? I'm not gonna use
your disgusting shirt.
[gasps] Shut up! It's clean.
I wash this thing every
single day, so use it!
Hm?
[sniffles]
[laughing]
Yeah! Let's go to
practice! Woo!
Right. Let's go.
[ASAHI laughs]
Swim club, swim club.
Yeah!
[inhales, exhales]
[FIRST YEARS]
We're sorry, sir!
[NATSUYA] You guys have a lot
of nerve skipping practice.
[IKUYA]
It's my fault.
I ran out of school earlier, and
everyone else only came after me
because they were
worried about me.
That's the reason we were late.
I'm very sorry, sir!
[gasps]
[ASAHI] No, I ran off without
thinking about anything!
I'm very sorry, sir!
[MAKOTO] And I should've
said something to you
before going after them.
I'm very sorry, sir!
Guys, what in the world
is wrong with you?
Did you all get hit in the head?
[IKUYA]
It's possible.
I did get tackled by the
stupidest guy in the world, so.
Hey! Shut up!
That would never have happened
if you hadn't been so confusing!
[IKUYA]
Yeah, well, intelligent people
wouldn't have been confused.
What?! You take that back.
I will, as soon as you
quit being stupid.
Ikuya. Ahh!
Stop! Let go of me!
Why are you so weird!
Get off!
[IKUYA]
Natsuya, listen.
I've realized that I've
been letting myself swim
in your shadow for a while.
But, I'm gonna stop it.
And about what you said
that made me so angry.
I get what you were doing now.
Okay.
Wait a second.
Why isn't Nao here?
Yeah. He's uh, well...
Nao, sir!
Hey, guys.
[ASAHI] What happened, are
you gonna die or something?
No. I told Natsuya
not to say anything.
[MAKOTO] Sir, are you
sure you're all right?
We heard you were
having surgery.
I am, but it's not something
to freak out about.
Looks like I'll be able to
leave as soon as it's over.
Why do you need to have surgery?
Detached retina.
It randomly started to
get really hard to see
out of my right eye last fall.
I thought it would eventually
get better,
so I tried to ignore it.
Didn't work, and now I
have to have surgery.
[MAKOTO]
Sir. Will you...
Uh, when will you be able
to come back to practice?
[NAO]
I can coach you guys right away.
But, I will have to take a break
from competing for a while.
This year, I won't be able
to swim in any races.
[gasps]
Oh! Hey, now,
don't make those faces,
everything will be fine.
No, I won't be able to
race in anything now.
But I can compete again
when I get to high school!
So you'll keep swimming?
I only started because Natsuya
kinda forced me to join, but...
It turned out I loved to swim.
Asahi. I remember
when I was first told
I wouldn't be able to race
for the rest of the year.
I was depressed for a while.
Once I realized it wasn't
forever, though,
I got over it pretty fast.
There was no point
in being impatient.
I know you're gonna swim
freestyle again.
Don't stress out about it.
Sometimes, we just have to wait.
Right!
[NAO] Makoto, you worry
about other people too much.
It's okay to be selfish
every so often. Also...
I have feeling Haruka might
feel you're a little too nosy.
[gasps] Haru! Do you?!
Ikuya, trust everyone
around you more.
If you stay inside your shell,
it won't do you any good.
That's true for swimming
and school.
Thank you, really.
But I... I understand now.
I'm glad.
Haruka.
Sir?
Stick to your convictions,
no matter what.
You get to swim free in the
relay and individual races.
Just don't let the past
determine your future.
[gasps]
All you have to do is that, and
I promise you'll be unbeatable.
Right.
[NAO] I know this is going
to sound immature,
and the last thing I want to do
is pressure you guys any more,
but since I can't swim,
do you think you can win for me?
[ALL inhale]
Yes, sir!
[NAO]
Oh! Hey, you don't have to yell!
[ASAHI laughs]
We should all run home together!
--[IKUYA] Why?
--[MAKOTO] What? Run home?
[ASAHI]
I don't know.
I really feel like moving
my body right now!
Just think of it like
extra training.
Come on, let's go!
[IKUYA]
Wait, Asahi!
Great, this is why guys
with muscles connected
directly to their brains
are the worst.
Hey, wait for us!
Come on.
[exhales]
[BOYS panting]
[HARUKA pants]
All right, I got first place!
[ASAHI]
Haru?!
Haru!
[MAKOTO]
Haru, are you okay?!
What's wrong? Do you feel
sick or something?
Haruka! Can you hear me?
[HARUKA] I said... stop
calling me Haruka.
Haruka! Haruka, look at me!
[ALL gasp]
Uh, where am I?
[MAKOTO whimpers]
Haru!
You've only been eating
mackerel, huh?
You're in the hospital.
Apparently, you passed out
from low blood sugar.
That's what the doctor said.
Wow, low blood sugar?
Haruka, you were supposed
to be eating well.
Why didn't you tell me
what was going on?
[HARUKA]
I'm sorry.
[MAKOTO'S MOM]
I was so worried about you.
Who knew? Hm...
Looks like you're human,
too, huh, Haru?
Huh...?
Heh.
[IKUYA]
What're you even saying?
Oh, good. Look who's awake.
You'll be able to
get out of here
as soon as that IV finishes up.
Although, you should go home,
take it easy for
the rest of the day.
You're a growing boy, make
sure you get enough food.
'Kay.
All right, I'll go take care
of the discharge paperwork
and then head out
to the grocery store.
You boys can get Haru
home for me, can't you?
[MAKOTO]
Mm-hm.
[door slides]
[footsteps]
[doorbell rings]
[MAKOTO]
Haru! I brought over some food!
[gasps] Did everyone
have to come with you?
Here, this is for you.
We're so excited to be here!
Uh...
[MAKOTO, IKUYA]
Thanks for letting us in!
You don't mind if I borrow
your kitchen, do you?
Hold on. What for?
You passed out because you
wouldn't take care of yourself,
which is a serious problem.
So we are gonna
stay here a while.
Together, we figure
we'll make sure
you don't pull that crap again.
How lucky are you, right?
[gasping]
Oh, and your mom said
she'll be back in three days
and that she's cool
with us staying.
We're not leaving!
Might as well suck it up.
Yeah. He's right, Haru.
Our parents are
okay with it, too,
so you're not
getting out of this.
Just wait in the living
room for us, 'kay?
No one asked me though.
[IKUYA] Asahi, you're in the
way. Would you move?
[ASAHI]
I am? Oh, sorry.
[IKUYA]
Wait, what're you doing?
You're cutting
before peeling it!
How stupid can you be?!
Don't be rude! Plus, what
is with these shapes?
They're awful!
[gasping] No, it's
overflowing! And hot!
[IKUYA, ASAHI yelp]
You're gonna burn us!
[MAKOTO]
Oh, sorry.
This is what we made, but um,
that stuff was made by my mom.
Well, eat up.
Thank you for this food!
Thanks for the food.
Here, for you.
What do you think,
is it any good?
It's not bad.
[MAKOTO laughs]
You always hide how
you really feel. Why?
You do, too.
Sorry, what?
What, who just said that?
This is coming from the guy who
can't think before anything?
You're such a child.
Remember that misunderstanding
from earlier.
Hey! You were the one crying
all over the place like a baby!
Uh. I... No.
You're lying!
I wasn't like that,
and you know it!
[ASAHI] Oh, really?
You weren't like that?
[IKUYA] Don't talk to me
in that stupid voice!
[MAKOTO]
Come on, you guys. Knock it off.
--[HARU] Heh.
--[ALL gasp]
[IKUYA, ASAHI]
He laughed!
I did not.
I just watched it happen!
Admit it! You laughed.
Yep, you did.
You saw nothing.
Yes, I did!
Sometimes, you really can be
the most adorable thing ever,
Haru. Fact.
Shut up. Can you just eat?
[ASAHI] It feels like we're
at an overnight school trip.
[IKUYA] Will you stop talking
and go to sleep. Loud.
[ASAHI] What a surprise
you're acting like a parent.
It's not my fault I can't sleep.
Try harder. We have
school tomorrow.
[ASAHI] Mm! Yeah, but I really
want to go swimming!
[IKUYA] Weird,
considering you're usually
just trying not to drown.
[ASAHI]
I know, but...
...I feel back to normal now.
What?
[ASAHI]
You see...
The second I saw Haru's
freestyle, I was like,
there's a guy who's way,
way better than me.
And I felt kinda like I
swallowed my heart.
I've been thinking about it,
and I know that yeah,
he really is better than me.
And that's what helped
you get back to normal?
[ASAHI] No, what helped
was seeing Haru pass out.
I realized, "This guy's just
a regular human, too."
Wasn't that already obvious?
[laughs]
[ASAHI] I know now that I let
my own pride get in my way,
but, seeing Haru being,
well, not perfect did make
me feel a lot better.
Now, I can accept myself
even if I'm not that good.
However! I'm not
planning to lie down
and let you keep beating
me so watch your back!
I'll catch up with you soon!
Fine, do what you want.
Yeah. Just know
you've been warned.
Good work.
Nice to know you thought at
least one thing through.
You screwing with me?!
Calm down.
You really should be proud
of yourself, though.
It takes a lot to admit
that stuff, right?
I guess it does, yeah. [gasps]
But you might need to admit
some stuff to yourself
to get to the root
of this problem.
Oh. That's it.
I think I did what that
one kid was talking about.
What kid?
This guy from the other day
who gave me some
advice at the library.
--What was he like?
--Wore glasses.
What? Like for real?
We're supposed to know what
he's like with that information?
[laughs]
[MAKOTO] When we were
in elementary school,
Haru and I got to be on this
amazing medley relay team.
Makoto.
Iwatobi SC, right?
Yep. Our teammates
were this kid Nagisa,
and another kid, named Rin.
His name came up at
the practice swim meet.
I thought back then that was
the best team I'd compete
with in my whole life.
And we did win.
But then we graduated,
and we were suddenly not
together anymore.
I didn't believe I could be
on a team better than that.
Which is why I didn't feel too
confident about the relay.
I mean, this may only be me,
but it didn't seem like
either you or Haruka
were even tryin' to take
the relay seriously.
[gasps] Sorry.
I don't get it.
[MAKOTO, HARUKA, IKUYA]
Uh?
[ASAHI]
If it was this super great team,
then why are you being
all negative about it?
You'd be happy you got
to swim with those guys.
And it doesn't really matter
if our team isn't as good.
Um, that's not very fair
to you and Ikuya.
Why not?
Don't take this the wrong way,
but I think my team at my
old SC was the best, too.
Who cares?
Let's work to make this team
better than all our other teams.
[BOTH gasp]
[sighs] All right. Night.
Don't try to reason with him.
He's stupid.
Hey, are you picking
a fight with me?!
[IKUYA] I used to think I was
fine as long as I could swim
by myself, that my personal
best was enough.
Now, though,
all I want to do
is to swim a medley
relay with you jerks.
[ASAHI, MAKOTO gasp]
[laughing]
[snores]
[CROWD chattering]
[NATSUYA]
All right, this is it!
The official meet.
Your times will guide you
for the rest of the year.
So, do your best, okay?
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Sir!
[NATSUYA]
Iwatobi, fight!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Yeah!
[MALE REFEREE A]
Ready...
--[beeps]
--[CROWD] Go!
Wish me luck! Later!
Good luck!
[NATSUYA]
Uh?
It's almost time for the relay.
So guys, feel good?
--Yes, sir!
--Yes!
Yes!
And Haruka?
Before, when I was on
another relay team,
it was really special to
both Makoto and me.
That's the reason I didn't
want to swim in a relay
with any other team.
And now?
I believe things have
changed for me a bit.
Today, I want to swim
a great relay
with these guys on this team.
[BOTH gasp]
Good. Then swim a great relay.
But this time,
make sure you win!
[MAKOTO, IKUYA]
Right!
[ASAHI]
You can count on us, sir!
[IKUYA] Leave it to stupid
to run by the pool.
[NAO laughs]
[NATSUYA]
Hm?
I'm never gonna quit teaching
as long as I get to experience
moments like these.
[NATSUYA]
Mm? Yeah, that's great and all,
but you still have some of
your own swimming left to do.
I'm already tired of waiting.
[NAO chuckles]
I'll be back.
You better not swim half-assed
like you did the other day.
You do, you'll be sorry.
Don't worry. You'll lose.
Heh.
[gasps] It's Haru's team!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER A]
Next up for today's meet
will be the boys' 400
meter medley relay!
Go, Makoto!
[IKUYA]
Yeah, get us ahead early!
Sure!
[MALE REFEREE A]
Ready...
--[beeps]
--[CROWD cheers]
[ASAHI]
Yes! Awesome start!
Go, Makoto, go!
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Makoto!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Makoto!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Push it! Push it, push it,
push it, push it, Makoto!
Tachibana!
Iwatobi!
[ASAHI]
Makoto's in the lead!
Push it! Go, Mako!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Makoto!
[MALE SWIMMER B] Push it!
Push it, push it, push it...
He's fast.
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go...
Hey, don't lose the vontage
he got for us, 'kay?
Who do you think
you're talking to?
And the word's not "vontage,"
you idiot, it's "advantage."
So stupid.
[whines]
Ikuya!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Ikuya!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go,
let's go, let's go,
let's go, Ikuya!
Wouldja look at that.
He's gotten so much better.
Go, Ikuya!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Ikuya!
Ikuya! Ikuya!
--[MALE SWIMMER B] Go! Fight!
--[IWATOBI SWIMMERS] Ikuya.
Come on, Ikuya! Fight!
Asahi! You can do it!
[HARUKA] All you have to
do is swim back here.
You guys. Thank you.
[HARUKA, MAKOTO gasp]
Y'know. I'm happy I'm
swimming with this team.
It's way more fun
than I expected.
Feels same to you, right?
[BOTH gasp]
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Push it! Push it, push it,
push it, push it, Ikuya!
Asahi!
Go, Asahi! Go!
Hurry up and get
back here, stupid!
Did you see how much better
his start was this time?
He's completely
in sync with you.
[grunts] Not that I want that.
[ASAHI'S SISTER]
Oh? Not bad, bro.
You ready?
Haru, we'll be right here
waiting here for you.
I know.
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Asahi!
Haruka!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Haruka!
[IWATOBI SWIMMERS]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Haruka!
[MALE SWIMMER B]
Push it! Push it, push it,
push it, push it, Har...
[ALL cheering]
[gasps]
[CROWD cheering]
[MAKOTO]
Haru!
[IKUYA gasping]
[ASAHI gasping]
[BOYS]
Haru! [laughing]
Yes, that was the best!
Go us!
Wow! We were amazing.
[MAKOTO]
First place?!
[ASAHI]
We did it!
[BOYS chattering]
Yes, yes, yes!
[NAGISA laughs]
They won! [laughs]
[MAKOTO]
Amazing! This was amazing!
[ALL laughing]
Huh?
[RIN]
Dear Sosuke. How are you?
I'm all right, I guess.
I think I've finally gotten
used to living here.
At first, the language barrier
made it really difficult.
I did my best with
gestures and pictures,
but no one could understand me.
Like one day, I drew a
picture of a cherry tree,
and someone brought me a mop.
I wanted to come home so bad.
Did you know there are kangaroos
just on the street here?
I wanted to touch one,
but I was told not to
because they kick real hard.
Everyone at the swim club
here is super fast.
I lose every day.
I wish I could say
I win all the time,
but the guys here are
even bigger than Makoto,
so there's a pretty big
difference in power.
I'm workin' on it, though.
I actually got put in
the slowest class for now.
I feel frustrated
about it all the time.
What if I eventually
get used to it?
What if the things that bother
me so much stop bothering me.
That's a scary thought.
I'm never gonna give up!
I will get faster!
I'll swim faster than anyone!
Hey, remember the relay?
I'll never forget that team.
How could I?
That guy still swims
in front of me.
All I want...
is to be that fast.
I just want to hurry up, and
be able to swim like Haru!
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA]
Rin.
I do, too.
I really do.
I want to swim like you.
[SOSUKE] That letter was
originally addressed to you.
But I thought it was yours.
Nope. Look again more closely.
The part saying "that guy"?
It used to say "you"
but he erased it.
It's faint, but it was you.
[gasps]
[SOSUKE] Knowing Rin, I'm
sure he wanted to send it,
but got too embarrassed.
He did spend the time
writing it, though, so,
he just sent it to me.
That's Rin, you know?
When I first read the letter,
it seemed kinda weird.
I mean, why bother mentioning
Tachibana to me?
Mostly, the writing
was too one-sided.
Almost like he wrote
that stuff knowing
he'd never receive
an answer back.
He knows my personality.
He'd never have written
like that to me.
You can keep the letter.
Are you sure?
Yeah, it's yours, that's
what he wanted anyway.
I'll win on the individual.
Later.
[MAKOTO]
Haru!
Let's go!
Yeah.