[SPARK] What Parn told me
is starting to ring true.
[PARN] Don't become a man
who lives only for the duty
that's given to him.
[SPARK] It's my decision
to make this journey.
I swear I'll recover the
two keys. And also...
Is something wrong, Spark?
Neese... I swear that
I will protect you.
Thanks.
[NARRATOR]
In pursuit of the Staff of Life
and the Soul Crystal Ball,
Spark and the others,
in the ship supplied
by King Etoh of Valis,
arrive at the shores of Kanon,
gateway to the dark
island of Marmo.
[SPARK]
We finally made it to Kanon...
Isn't it great to have real
ground under your feet again?
You gotta love this land.
Aw, what's wrong? Did the boat
ride make you seasick, Garrack?
[GARRACK growls]
[ALDO]
Lady Neese, please wait.
[NEESE]
Huh?
[ALDO] You shouldn't let
your clothes get wet.
[NEESE] Ah... Ah!
It's all right, Aldanova!
I don't mind getting
a little wet.
"You should let your
clothes get wet."
Yeah, right. Somebody should
be saying that to me.
[yelps]
What do you think you're doing?
Get a move on.
[LEAF growls]
In that case, you may
travel as far as Kanon
aboard one of our
military ships.
May the gods of Light watch
over and protect you.
[SPARK] I shall be grateful
to you forever, King Etoh.
[GARRACK]
Okay?
[SPARK]
Huh?
[GARRACK] What're we going to do
now that we're here, Captain?
Is there a need to ask?
We make our way through
Kanon and head straight
for the island of Marmo.
[RYNA moans]
This breeze feels good...
Kinda tingles, doesn't it, Ryna?
The air in Kanon has a
character all its own.
Kanon is a fertile land
of lush greenery.
It's prevailing winds come
from a different direction
than the desert winds of Flaim.
[GARRACK]
A different direction, eh?
So, do you think this new wind
will blow some luck our way?
We sure could use a little.
But I think if we keep heading
east, we should be okay.
[NEESE] This path will
take us straight to Roodo.
They'll head that way, too.
Whoever has the crystal ball
and the Staff of Life,
they'll have to find a major
port if they're going to make
the crossing into Marmo.
I agree. Roodo is
the most likely place
for us to find a way
to Marmo as well.
Hold on. Remember what King Etoh
said about Kanon's free army.
If they can help us,
then we should find them.
He's right. The free army is
our only ally here in Kanon.
They've probably got the latest
information on the Marmo.
Perhaps, but we must get to
Roodo as quickly as we can...
...and finish the job
we came here to do.
We cannot afford a delay.
[LEAF]
Look, I know we're in a hurry,
but did you really have
to pick this road?!
The Marmo army could never
travel on a road like this.
It may not be the easiest
way, but it is the safest.
[LEAF] Yeah, but I'm not exactly
a mountain goat, you know?!
Come on, just do your best.
[growls]
[GARRACK]
Quit your bellyaching and climb.
Once we've passed these hills,
there's nothing but forests.
[LEAF]
Hey, you! I thought I told you
to keep your hands
off me, right?!
Listen here, I got
somethin' to say!
So young, so very young...
What is with everyone?!
[ALDO]
Lady Neese, please! Wait.
[NEESE pants]
You're so tired. Please, allow
me to carry you on my back.
It's all right, Aldo.
Don't worry about me.
I can make it...
I'm sorry that we're
pushing you so hard.
Just hang on a little
longer, Neese. Come on.
[NEESE]
But Spark!
[NEESE pants]
[LEAF pants]
[LEAF]
I made it...
Yeah!
Oh...
Out of breath already? And you
call yourself a mercenary?
Come on now, Leaf--
Huh? What happened here?
It's horrible...
[SPARK grunts]
[GREEVUS] The rich, green fields
of Kanon... burned and barren.
It's truly a crime
against nature itself.
The kingdom of Kanon...
reduced to this empty shell...
I can't believe it...
Who could've done this?
Are Marmo soldiers this bad?
[NEESE gasps]
[SPARK growls]
Lady Neese! Are you all right?!
[NEESE]
Yes.
Oh, please forgive me!
I'll never let you out
of my sight again!
It's all right, Aldo.
Typical of the Marmo. Using
monsters to fight for them.
[GARRACK] So now we've got
monsters to deal with.
I bet the Marmo have a
lot more of them, too.
Don't even joke about that.
[GARRACK]
It doesn't matter.
The kingdom of Kanon
was once a paradise.
Now it's just a
burned up memory.
[GARRACK sighs]
[LEAF]
Will you quit bellyaching?
I found a tree full
of these nearby.
Maybe we'll all feel better
if we eat something.
Catch!
Thank you. Perhaps you're right.
Here.
Good old Kanon! A land ready
to fill my belly right up!
Just like the stories say.
[LEAF]
Here, Neese.
Thanks, Leaf.
[ALDO] Just a moment,
please, Lady Neese.
Eating food from an unknown
source could make you very sick
and we wouldn't want that.
[NEESE]
But Aldonova, I--
I'll make sure your food
is safely prepared.
If anything were
to happen to you,
I would never be able to
face Master Slayn again.
Oh. Right...
They're just fine...
Now, here you go.
Huh?! Huh?! Lady Neese!
Lady Neese!
Where did you go?! Lady Neese!
[SPARK]
So... The Marmo threat is great.
Huh? Who's that? Oh... what
can we do for you, Neese?
[NEESE pants]
I thought I'd take
over the watch.
You both must be very tired.
What are you talking
about, Neese?
We're fine. There's nothing
to worry about,
so just get some rest.
But I... Even I can stand guard,
Spark. I want to help!
I swore that I would
protect you, Neese.
Now you should just
let me do my job.
Unless you think I'm not going
to be very good at it.
[NEESE] So you'll just
keep me in a shell...
[SPARK]
Huh?
It's not fair! I can-- [gasps]
[growling]
What was that?!
Here they come...
[TROLLS growling]
[ALDO]
Lady Neese!
Yeah, I figured things were
getting too easy for us.
[growling continues]
[MARMO CAPTAIN]
We've been waiting for you.
You guys are pretty dumb!
Especially for free army!
Great! This muscle-head thinks
we're members of the free army!
Well, their enemies
are our enemies.
You're not free army, but we
can kill you just the same.
My Daybreak Mercenaries would
love to take your heads!
[GARRACK] Mercenaries, huh? Then
allow me to introduce myself!
I am the Blue Meteor!
[GARRACK grunting]
Man, Garrack sure does
know how to raise hell.
I think he could use some help.
[GREEVUS growls]
[GARRACK grunting]
Aldo, we should
circle behind them.
[ALDO]
Right!
Hey, wait for me!
[laughs]
Huh...?
Hey, we can't let those
three get away! After them!
[TROLLS growling]
[GARRACK growls]
[TROLL yells]
[GARRACK]
Huh...?
Hey.
[GARRACK]
Huh?
A little thank you
might be nice.
[TROLLS growling]
Too many of them...
It's numbers over skills.
"I summon the glittering
spirits of the light!
Gather and let your
form be shown!"
[TROLLS grunting]
That wasn't too tough.
[gasps]
[GREEVUS growls]
Wow! Greevus!
Don't ever get careless, Leaf!
You don't have to
jump down my throat!
[panting]
What a high cliff...
[MARMO CAPTAIN]
Hold it right there.
I can't believe you actually
ran here to try to escape.
Now I know for sure
you're not free army.
You're just too stupid.
[MARMO CAPTAIN]
Kill 'em.
[SPARK yells]
[NEESE pants]
Oh, Spark!
Aldo, put 'em to sleep!
Right!
"Gentle atmospheres
that bring sleep...
O, let your power
enter their bodies
and cast them
into deep slumber!"
Who the hell are these guys?
Guess I'll just have
to call the big boy.
[whistles]
[growling]
[roars]
--[RYNA gasping]
--[GARRACK] What the--?!
I don't like the sound of that.
I think it came from over there.
Hey, where did Spark go?
[crashing]
[roars]
An ogre!
Go on, be as brutal as you want.
We don't need anyone who
challenges the Marmo.
Now go kill 'em.
--[ALDO] Lady Neese!
--[SPARK] Neese!
"Great manna of all creation!
Become a mighty shield
to protect us!"
[ALDO screams]
[NEESE]
Aldonova!
Neese! Run for it! I'll
keep him away from you!
Spark!
[SPARK yells, grunts]
[NEESE]
Spark!
[SPARK]
Neese... You've got to run...
No way.
Egh! Lady Neese!
[SPARK]
Run, Neese!
"Holy Marfa, mother
of the Earth...
Become a shield to protect us!"
[NEESE grunts]
[OGRE growls]
What the hell?!
I can't believe that little
girl just beat him!
[NEESE gasps] Spark!
Neese... Now's your
chance to get away...
Hurry up...
I won't go. I can fight!
I can fight against them!
No, you can't.
You're not a warrior.
Fighting is what we're
supposed to do.
Protecting you is
my duty as a knight.
Enough about your duty!
[SPARK]
Huh...?
Enough already.
I want to protect you .
Because I'm friend, Spark.
[sniffs] I'm your friend...
Thanks, Neese.
[roars]
So, you think you're cute
with those magic tricks?
Not this time. Now kill 'em!
[roars]
Neese!
What is it, Spark?
Do you think that you can hold
this monster in one place?
Huh?
Can you do it, Neese?!
Yes, I can.
[NEESE] "Holy Marfa, mother
of the Earth, I beg of you!
Restrain this evil one!"
[OGRE grunts]
Impossible...
All right!
[yells]
[OGRE groans]
[MARMO CAPTAIN]
Huh?!
[MARMO CAPTAIN
whimpers, screams]
[NEESE]
Spark! Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Thank goodness you're unharmed.
[NEESE] Aldonova! You're
alive! Are you all right?
Huh? Yes.
[GARRACK]
Hey, you guys okay?!
[SPARK]
Yeah, we're all right.
[LEAF gasps]
Oh! This is amazing!
These wagons are
loaded with food!
The Marmo... They must've been
protecting their supplies.
Hey, the Marmo take pretty
good care of themselves.
[GREEVUS]
Grain, meat, vegetables...
The Marmo must've
stolen this food
from the good people
of Kanon. Damn them!
Well, this will all go
to waste if we leave it!
Now... Well... [giggles]
Hey, you! I had my eye
on that one! Now let go!
I'm so sorry, pal, but
victory goes to the swift.
Hey! Get back here!
[footsteps]
[SPARK]
Um... Neese?
Ah. Yes?
Look, about...
[NEESE]
Yes?
About before? I thank you.
You saved my life.
No, don't thank me.
It's only natural to protect
your friends, right?
[RYNA]
Spark, catch!
[yelps]
[RYNA giggles]
Here.
Why, thank you.
Delicious.
[SPARK]
Mm-hmm.
[SPARK gasps]
[MAN] Those supplies belong
to the people of Kanon!
They don't belong to you Marmo!
Marmo?
Oh, give me a break!
Now they think we're Marmo!
I claim these supplies in the
name of the Kanon free army.
[SPARK]
The Kanon free army?!
Hold it! You're wrong!
We aren't Marmo!
Wait.
We're all from Flaim, and
we've just come from Valis.
Don't try to trick me!
[SPARK]
But it's not a trick! It's true!
I'm carrying a letter from
King Etoh! I'll show it to you!
[VOICE]
A letter from King Etoh?
[gasps]
I got to see this for myself.
[gasps] Can it really be?!
The free knight... Parn!
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've
all been waiting for,
the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
[SPARK] All right! I can't
believe how lucky we were
to find this totally
happening beach!
I just love the summer
time at the beach!
Now I can relax
and have fun! Yup!
[NEESE]
Spark! Spark! Come on in!
The water feels great! [giggles]
[LITTLE DRAGON squawks]
Huh?
[giggles]
Huh...? [screams]
[screams]
[NEESE] Help, Spark!
It's a freakin' shark!
Hang on, Neese!
I'm a knight in training
and it's my duty to protect you!
Uh-oh... This is not
a sword... Wahh...
Help! Do something,
you freakin' sissy!
No! Ma... ma...!
[BOTH grunting]
Ow...
Brave knight my ass.
Huh...?
Don't look, Neese...
Huh?
[shrieks]
That's no shark!
Yeah! That makes Jaws look cute!
[LITTLE DRAONG squawks]
[VOICE]
Ouch.
Thatta boy!
[PARN]
Hey, wait a second!
[NEESE]
Huh?
Long time no see, Spark!
[SPARK] Agh! It's an old
pervert! Run away! Run away!
I just wanted to give
him the magic sword...
That's why I've been swimming
around for so long...
He said I'm old...
[NEESE, SPARK]
We'll be seeing you!
[NEESE]
Amid the hardship of battle,
we take a moment's
rest at a banquet
in the fortress
of the free army.
Here, I can finally relax.
I know I shouldn't
get used to this,
but, oh, how I wish
it would last.
This peaceful night
with Spark...
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War :
Chronicles of
the Heroic Knight :
"Counterattack...
The Stolen Last Hope."