[RANDY, RYNA panting]
Randy! Hurry!
[RANDY]
We've got the worst luck!
Where'd these guys come from?!
[DARK ELVES laughing]
I summon the
power of the gnomes.
[DARK ELF A chuckles]
[RANDY groans]
Randy!
[RANDY]
What the...?
[RANDY grunts]
Dammit!
Ryna, please,
just leave me here!
[RYNA]
No way! C'mon.
[DARK ELF A] "Evil spirits from
the forest of darkness..."
[RANDY]
Forget me! Just get out of here!
Hang on! There! Now!
Up. C'mon!
[RANDY gasps]
[RANDY screams]
[RYNA]
Randy!
[gasps]
What is that feeling?
[SPARK] There it is.
The southern fortress!
Yeah. We finally made it.
And now we can all
get a little rest.
I hope there's some news
about the group of Dark Elves
who managed to steal
the Soul Crystal Ball.
Yes. We should hurry up.
I can't wait
for somethin' to eat.
A warm bath for me. Ahh...
[SPARK]
I am Spark.
Captain of the pursuit team,
sent by King Kashue.
[GUARD A] We've been
expecting you. This way.
Huh?!
Huh...
This must be the
southern fort...
[NEESE]
That feeling I had before...
I know it came from this place.
Something's wrong...
[SPARK]
Any news about the intruders?
[GUARD B]
We've got two mercenaries here
who say they saw what
appeared to be Dark Elves.
They aren't citizens
of Flaim, though...
[SPARK] Eyewitnesses?! We've got
to speak to them right now.
You can't be serious.
We didn't even get
a chance to sit down.
What's your point?
My point is, I'm hungry.
And now I'm going to
sit and enjoy a meal.
And so am I.
But... Leaf?!
[LEAF] But first,
I wanna get washed up.
I've got sand in places you
wouldn't want to know about!
[GARRACK]
Sorry, Captain.
Uh... But!
[LEAF]
Of course,
we won't mind if you go
and talk to them first.
Okay? See ya!
You don't mind...
Hey, who's the captain here?!
How did I ever get
stuck with those two?
Don't get so mad.
This is the way mercenaries are,
so they can be ready
to fight at any time.
So this is how
mercenaries usually act?!
Yes. Most of them.
Well, I shouldn't have
to put up with that!
You've got to
get over it, Spark.
These people are your comrades.
Comrades or not, they should
still respect their captain.
I wanted to get after those Dark
Elves as quickly as possible!
[SPARK sighs]
[GREEVUS exhales]
Huh?
[sighs]
Comrades, huh?
[NEESE]
A star of fate?
[SLAYN]
Yes. Your very own star.
One you can't find unless
you travel with comrades.
[NEESE] And Mother was
your star, wasn't she?
[SLAYN]
I have two stars now.
And the little one shines
just like its mother.
You're my little star, Neese.
[NEESE laughs]
And now the time
has come, my daughter,
for you to make
a distant journey.
To find my own star of destiny?
[SLAYN] My dear, your journey
will not be a pleasant one.
But as long as you have comrades
who will help you fight,
I know you will find your star.
My very own star of destiny...
Comrades... And my own
star of destiny...
I wonder if I'll ever find them.
[RANDY groaning]
[GUARD C] There are some
people here to question you.
Come with me.
Uh... Ryna...
I know, Randy. Don't worry.
I've managed to keep them
in the dark about us so far.
I know I can do this.
Just lie back, and try to rest.
Here she is, sir.
Where are the Dark Elves?!
How did you see them?!
Uh, well...!
[GREEVUS]
Spark!
Calm yourself.
Uh. Right.
[exhales]
Please forgive me.
My name is Spark,
and I'm a knight in training
from the Kingdom of Flaim.
Ryna is my name.
My partner and I were on our
way to Blade to look for work.
Where is your partner now?
He's resting in the barracks.
They hurt him pretty bad.
And we've got no one on our
staff who can help to heal him.
I'll do whatever
I can to help him.
I thank you.
Please, come with me.
Will you please tell
me what happened?
Yes.
It was the night before last.
We were walking,
on our way to Blade...
[splash]
[RYNA] They suddenly
appeared from the river.
[DARK ELVES chattering]
[RYNA]
Dark Elves! Five of them!
[SPARK]
From the river?
[ALDO] Dark Elves can
move through water.
Once they left the desert,
they probably used the
river to move south.
[RYNA] They attacked as
soon as they saw us.
With five against two, we knew
we didn't have a chance.
We tried to out run them...
...but it didn't work.
[SPARK]
A monster?!
Yes. It just sprang
up from the ground.
[LEAF]
I know all about that monster.
[ALL]
Huh?
[SPARK]
Leaf! Are you sure?
[LEAF]
Watch this.
"Power of the gnomes!
I command you to come!"
[GUARD D groaning]
That's the one.
Yeah, all elves know how
to do shamanist magic.
All right now.
Break the spell. Please, Leaf?
Don't worry. The spell
will vanish all by itself.
[groaning]
All right now, let me
take a look at this wound.
[GREEVUS gasps]
What is that thing?!
[GREEVUS]
First, let's get you healed.
"Myrii, Almighty God of War.
I summon your power to
heal this man's wounds."
[gasping]
[SPARK] Now Ryna, you say you
encountered the Dark Elves here,
then, if we set out right now,
we could probably
catch up with them
before they get much further.
[GARRACK]
Before we do anything,
there's just one thing
I want to know.
[ALL]
Huh?
Why did they let you survive?
I sure as hell wouldn't have
wanted any witnesses left alive.
I have no idea why!
The Dark Elves disappeared right
after they wounded Randy.
That sounds made up.
Why would she make
this whole thing up?!
What makes you
think she's not, sir?
Look into her eyes! I know
she's telling the truth!
Oh. Her eyes.
Must be nice to be so young.
[SPARK]
Wha--?! How dare you insult me!
Boy, you two sure know how to
waste a lot of time, don't you?
Why can't we just work together?
More like a team?
We've only been
companions for two days.
That's a lot to ask.
But none of you are taking
this seriously enough!
[ALDO] The Dark Elves stole
the Soul Crystal Ball!
One of the Destroyer's tools.
Don't they know what's
at stake here?
The entire future of Lodoss
is riding on this mission!
Everybody out! Now!
[ALL gasp]
[MONSTER roars]
[gasps]
Oh, my!
[MONSTER hissing]
[SPARK]
What is that thing?!
[GREEVUS] I don't know!
I've never anything like it!
But it's definitely their trap!
"Their trap"? Do you mean
the Dark Elves'?
I do.
[RANDY groaning]
[gasps]
[GREEVUS] They Dark Elves
implant the monster
into a human body.
It begins to grow rapidly
as soon as a healing
spell is used on it.
[SPARK]
What do you make of it?
It must be one of the hell
spawn from Marmo's dark forest.
What about Randy?!
He's already been
absorbed by the monster.
There is no way
I could've saved him.
You mean...
There's no way we can help him?
In order to kill the monster,
we have no choice
but to kill the host.
[RYNA gasping]
[GUARDS screaming]
Hey, Aldo, look out!
"M-M-Manna of all..." Uh!
[GARRACK]
Look out!
[ALDO whimpers]
I... I, uh... Um, I... I--
If this is the way
you're gonna fight,
then just stay out of the way!
Garrack, you watch what you say!
I've seen too many
of my comrades die
because of guys like him.
I don't wanna be one of them.
Manners don't matter
if you're dead.
Just shut up!
Let me try something.
"Great God Myrii,
who rules over war.
Gather the heroes here.
Grant us thy divine protection
in the coming battle,
Give us the resolve of iron
and the courage of fire!"
Do you feel the
courage inside you?
[ALDO]
Yes!
Everyone panics the first time.
It is Myrii's way of
testing all humans equally.
Right! Now let's stick together
and beat this monster!
Take care of her.
Right!
[GREEVUS]
In order to kill the monster,
we have no choice
but to kill the host.
Now!
[SPARK yells]
[GARRACK yells]
[LEAF yells]
[GREEVUS growls]
"Manna of all creation!
I command you to become
a blade of light,
and destroy him!"
[MONSTER growling]
Damn! We'll never stop them.
All right, Spark.
Now's the time.
You've got to make
it Randy's room.
[SPARK gasps]
If we don't attack
and kill the host,
we will never stop
this creature.
R-Right.
Aldo, I want you to use
your magic to distract him.
Yes, sir!
Greevus, you back
up the whole team.
[GREEVUS grunts]
I want you two to open
up a path for me.
And when you do, I'll go in!
How come you're talking all
the good jobs for yourself?
Oh, never mind him.
Are you sure you can do this?
I gave you an order!
Now carry it out!
[BOTH]
Yes, Captain!
Now! Let's go!
[GUARDS groaning]
[gasps]
[ALL yelling]
"Manna of all creation! Becomes
the fires of destruction!"
[MONSTER groans]
[grunts]
"Spirit of fire and flame!
Become a ball of white hot
light and destroy the enemy!"
[MONSTER roars]
Now's your chance, Spark!
Right!
[yelling]
[SPARK]
Huh?!
[groaning]
He's still alive...
[heartbeat]
[SPARK]
Can I really do this?
I know it will save
many other lives, but...
What are you waiting for,
Captain?! Kill him!
[SPARK whimpers]
Randy!
[GARRACK]
No! It's too dangerous.
Randy!
[roaring]
[SPARK yelling]
No, Randy!
What are you
waiting for, Captain?!
This guy's already dead.
Just kill him.
Yeah. But...!
[groaning]
[SPARK gasping]
Captain! Kill him now!
[GARRACK, RYNA scream]
Garrack! Are you all right?!
[LEAF groans]
[SPARK]
Leaf!
I have to do this!
[yelling]
[SPARK]
U-Uh.
Hey. What the...?
[gasping]
Oh, my. This is holy magic.
[gasps]
Huh?
It can't be her...
[NEESE] "Marfa, holy mother
of the Earth.
Purify his soul
and drive evil away."
The monster...
It's crumbling away.
Randy...
[RYNA]
Randy!
[GUARDS chattering]
Mm! This is delicious!
I guess there's nothing
that'll affect your appetite.
[GARRACK]
Hey, I'm a mercenary. Want some?
[LEAF]
No. You go right ahead.
[GREEVUS] Implanting a monster
like that in a human body.
A typical dirty trick
for a Dark Elf.
Oh, Randy... I hope
you're in a better place.
I swear. I will
avenge your death.
[inhales]
I will join them.
L-Lady Neese! What are
you doing here?!
You know her, Aldo?
Could that be it...? Oh...
Hey! Aldo!
[ALDO]
Uh. This is Lady Neese,
the daughter of Slayn,
the great wizard.
But I didn't even know that
Master Slayn had a daughter.
You've got a special name.
My grandmother was
a High Priestess
and one of the Six Heroes.
I was given my
name to honor her.
I see.
I would like to thank you for
helping to save us back there.
That was the will of Marfa,
the Goddess of the Earth.
Uh. By the way, what are you
doing out here all by yourself?
It is the will of the gods.
I am following a dark nightmare.
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've been
waiting for, the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
[SPARK]
Under orders from King Kashue,
I'm protecting Neese!
The granddaughter of... Uh...
Neese! One of the Six Heroes.
Along the way,
a gang of evil monsters
springs up to block our path!
But I won't lose! I am Spark,
knight of Flaim!
[yells]
[shouts]
[EVIL MONSTERS]
Ouch.
[SPARK] Well, at least the
introduction sounds cool,
but so far my duties as a
knight have been pretty lame.
Don't trip the trap, Spark!
[SPARK]
Huh? Ahh!
Heads up!
[SPARK muffled grumbles]
Oh, my. Ain't that a nice cake!
Hey! Who the heck
set this trap?!
Delish! Whoever made
this must be really d--
[screaming]
Yes. It's the sweet
trap of the Dark Elf...
Right there!
So, you finally noticed me.
It's the Dark Elf
with the sweet tooth!
You set that trap!
You better give me
those cookies there
if you want to make it
out of this forest alive.
Otherwise, you'll both be
drowning in sweet traps, huh?
Oh yeah?! I'll get you before--
[yelps]
[screaming]
Had enough there, cookie head?
Damn you!
Let's try some.
[DARK ELF]
Huh...?
They suck!
Your oven was too hot!
I can taste how hard you tried,
and the effort you put in!
But they still suck!
Huh...?! I'll try it again!
It's the will of Marfa.
[squawks]
Get these things... off me!
[NEESE, SPARK]
We'll be seeing you!
[SPARK] The journey of the
mysterious girl, Neese,
has begun.
I don't know what her goal is,
but my mission is quite clear!
Catching up with the Dark Elves,
we confront them in
an attempt to recover
the stolen crystal ball!
Next time,
on Record of Lodoss War:
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"Sallying Forth...
Pursuing a Dark Shadow."