[SPARK]
I'll go on ahead!
[yells]
Master Spark!
Now we've got a captain
who's really worth protecting!
[RYNA grunts]
[yells]
[groans]
[gasps]
[DARK ELF A] "Dark power,
come in to my hand!"
[SPARK grunting]
[DARK ELF B laughs]
[DARK ELF C chuckles]
[DARK ELVES grunting]
[SPARK]
Huh?!
[SPARK whimpering]
[GARRACK]
Captain!
[SPARK]
Huh?!
[DARK ELF A] "I summon
the tiny, invisible spirits..."
[SPARK]
Oh, no you don't!
Spread out!
[SPARK panting]
[SPARK]
We've finally found them!
There's no way I'll let
them escape now!
[SPARK yells]
[SPARK, DARK ELF C grunting]
[GREEVUS yells]
[SPARK grunts]
[DARK ELF A groans]
All right, now. Ya better hand
over the Soul Crystal Ball.
"Tiny spirits..."
[GREEVUS] Look out, Spark!
He's casting a spell!
[gasps]
--[SPARK] Huh?!
--[DARK ELF A laughs]
Watch out!
They got away!
[RYNA]
Something's wrong.
I'm sure they ran
this way, but--
[RYNA gasps]
[GARRACK]
Watch out.
They've made
themselves invisible.
[GARRACK] I know they're here.
I can sense their presence.
They're definitely close by.
[GARRACK]
But where?
Where?!
Ryna!
[RYNA gasps, groans]
[DARK ELF B]
"Spirits of invisibility,
let my form become your..."
[GARRACK yells]
Huh?
Ryna! Ryna! Speak to me! Ryna!
[DARK ELF B laughs]
[GARRACK] Damn you...
Show yourself, you coward!
[LEAF] Just stop your
tricks and come out!
I know you're using
invisibility spirits to hide.
Well, then. I do have
a few tricks of my own.
"Great spirits of the water,
answer my command!
Come to me and
become thy power!"
Damn! Come on. Show yourselves.
[GREEVUS]
Hmm?
[DARK ELF C laughs]
Huh?!
[gasps]
[SPARK grunting]
[growls]
A protection spell?
But who...? Huh?
Aldo!
"Myrii, Great God of War.
Hear my prayer and grant us the
strength of your divine power!
Transmit your power to my hand,
through my axe,
and be released!"
[DARK ELF A]
Ow!
[DARK ELF C yells]
You did it, Spark!
Yes... Somehow...
You can take care
of things here.
I've got to go now and
find the rest of them.
[GREEVUS]
Go ahead!
[SPARK]
Right!
I'm going to follow him.
[ALDO]
But! Lady Neese!
[swords clanging]
--[GARRACK grunting]
--[DARK ELF B laughing]
[GARRACK screams]
[panting]
[GARRACK]
Damn you!
[GARRACK] But you should know
better than to fool around
with mercenary from Flaim.
[GARRACK]
Now die!
[DARK ELF B groans]
I didn't need to see you.
I could sense you here.
So much for being invisible.
[DARK ELF B groans]
[GARRACK groans]
[SPARK]
Garrack!
[GARRACK]
Huh?
[SPARK]
You all right?!
[GARRACK]
Yeah. I'm okay. But Ryna's hurt.
[SPARK]
Ryna!
She's still breathing!
Somebody call Priest Greevus!
Now just leave this to me.
Are you all right?
[GARRACK]
Yeah.
"Holy Marfa,
mother of the Earth.
Heal this person's wounds."
[footsteps]
[GREEVUS]
Spark.
[SPARK]
Huh? Priest Greevus!
I performed a thorough
search on the three
Dark Elves we killed,
but none of them
had the Soul Crystal Ball.
I see, Greevus. Well, maybe the
one Leaf went after has it.
Uh! Where's Leaf? Where's Leaf?!
[LEAF]
I came up empty, too.
Hi.
Leaf! Where have you been?
I was getting worried.
Liar. You forgot all about me.
[GREEVUS]
That was quite a feat, Leaf.
It's no easy task
to kill a Dark Elf.
How were you able to see him?
[LEAF]
Oh, there was nothing to it.
[yells]
[GREEVUS]
So that's how you did it.
The crystal ball isn't here!
But that's impossible!
[GARRACK]
It actually makes sense.
[SPARK]
Huh?
Any thief worth his
name would never hold on
to stolen treasure for too long.
They probably passed
the Soul Crystal Ball
to someone else a while ago.
Then how do you
explain these guys?
[GARRACK] Decoys, intended to
lead us on a pointless chase.
Yeah. And I fell for it. Uh!
[bell tolls]
[RANDAL]
I see. Well done, Spark.
But don't look so sad.
You may not have
recovered the treasure,
but at least you took
care of the thieves.
Be proud of that.
But unless we recover
the Soul Crystal Ball,
our mission will
not be complete.
And because we fell for their
trick and killed them,
we have no chance of
finding the crystal now!
I'll send out a team of
our swiftest riders
to secure the latest
information from Akroyd.
Of course, Hiruto's defenses
will remain on high alert.
We will do all we can.
There is a real possibility
that the thieves passed along
the treasure somewhere in the
desert outside the city.
Perhaps there was a witness.
In any case, until we
have more information,
you should stay here
and get some rest.
Right.
[sighs]
And now Wagnard has
one of the keys...
[knocking]
[gasps]
Yes? Come in.
So, how's she doin'?
She's been through
the worst of it,
but she's still unconscious.
[door shuts, footsteps]
I'll watch her now.
Why don't you go get some rest?
There's some food ready in
the other room, if you like.
Why thank you. I think I will.
[SPARK]
What should I do now?
Should I listen
to Governor Randal
and just wait here for news?
No, that's a big waste of time.
Maybe we should give up on
finding the crystal
ball for now,
and focus on getting King
Kashue's message to Valis.
But if I do that, then...
[RYNA groans]
[SPARK]
Huh?
Where... am I...?
Hey there. It's about
time you woke up.
[RYNA]
Spark?
You're safely inside
Governor Randal's mansion.
But how?
Didn't the Dark Elves...?
Neese performed one of her
magical healing spells on you.
She says you probably
won't even have any scars.
But for now, I think you'd
better get some rest.
It'll be a while before
you get your strength back.
[RYNA]
You're a very kind man, Spark.
It is a knight's sworn duty
to be kind to all ladies.
Even knights in training?
[SPARK]
Yes, even me.
I want to go and tell the
others that you're awake.
Everyone's been so
worried about you.
Wait!
Please, Spark.
[SPARK]
Hm?
There is something
very important
that I must discuss with you.
[SPARK]
Huh?
I wasn't honest with you before,
when I said I was a mercenary.
The truth is... I'm a thief...
[gasps]
A thief?
[RYNA] I can't tell you how
sorry I am for deceiving you
all this time.
But... if my colleagues
in Blade found out, well...
I should already
be marked for death.
That's why I kept things secret.
But my wanting to avenge
Randy's death is true!
Believe me!
So, do you think
any less of me now?
[SPARK]
Well, being a thief is bad.
It's certainly nothing
to be proud of.
Well, it's better
than being a murderer.
[SPARK gasps]
[RYNA] Not everyone
can be as fortunate
as you have been, Spark.
When life's beaten
you down enough,
sometimes you've got to steal
and cheat just to survive.
I wonder what you're
going to do with me now--
Perhaps send me away,
or will you throw me in jail?
I would never abandon you.
In fact, I was hoping that you'd
consider staying on with us.
[gasps]
Now, I can't force you to come.
And your life may be in
danger from time to time.
But if I'm going to recover
the Soul Crystal Ball,
I'm going to need the
help of a clever thief.
[RYNA laughs]
Um. Uh. What is it?
So, you say you need
me because I'm a thief.
Is that the only reason?
Uh! Um... Well, uh--
You've also become a good
friend to all of us, too.
Uh... So perhaps you'd like
to stick around for that?
Good. Any other reason?
[SPARK]
Uh. No. That's it.
I'll go tell the
others that you're okay!
[RYNA]
Uh...
[door slams]
[RYNA laughs]
Ah! Mah!
[LEAF slurping]
Ahh!
There's nothing better than a
good meal after a good fight!
[GARRACK, LEAF grunting]
[groans]
[LEAF]
Heh!
[GARRACK]
Hm?
Captain?
What's wrong, Spark?
Is Ryna all right?
She sure is. In more
ways than you know...
She's doing fine now!
[LEAF]
Really...?!
What are you
talking about, Leaf?
[LEAF]
Captain, you're blushing!
Uhh! Uh... You must
be imaging things!
No I'm not.
Well, it looks as if there's no
need reason to worry anymore.
[ALDO]
Lady Neese?
I'm going to bring Miss Ryna
something good to eat.
Her wounds have healed,
but she's lost a lot of blood.
What she needs
now is nourishment.
She's quite a girl,
that Lady Neese.
Yeah. She handles
herself really well.
Not a bit like our captain here.
Am I right?
Oh, shut up.
[NEESE whimpering]
[NEESE]
No!
[NEESE gasps]
[WAGNARD chanting]
[WAGNARD] I've been
waiting for you, Doorway.
[NEESE]
You're...
[gasps]
You're Wagnard!
So, the young priestess
remembers my name.
I'm honored.
How dare you invade
my mind like this!
What are you trying
to do, Wagnard?!
Reviving Kardis the Destroyer
will annihilate
the entire world!
It's total madness!
[WAGNARD] Your feelings on the
matter are beside the point,
I'm sorry to say.
Neese, I need your body
to serve as the doorway.
Now, won't you please come along
with me to the dark island?
No! I refuse!
I have no intention
of helping you, Wagnard!
[WAGNARD laughs]
[NEESE screaming]
[gasps]
[LEAF] Neese! What's wrong?!
Open the door! Neese!
[SPARK]
What's wrong?!
[LEAF] I don't know!
I can't get the door open!
I'll handle this!
Everyone, just stand back!
[yells]
[SPARK]
No, wait!
[ALL gasp]
[GREEVUS yells]
[SPARK gasping]
[SPARK] What the...?
Hey. What's going on here?
[SPARK]
Neese...
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've
been waiting for,
the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
[SPARK, NEESE scream]
[BLACK DRAGON roars]
Spark, do something!
I think I just did!
Just kill it already!
Kill? Now there's a thought!
[SPARK]
How did I manage to get us lost
in the Black Dragon's dungeon?
I bet this wouldn't happen
to a real knight of Flaim...
So they've fallen
right into my trap.
Heh, heh.
All right, now, take care
of them there, Black Dragon!
[SPARK, NEESE scream]
Now's my chance! He'll need
some time to recharge!
[BLACK DRAGON roars]
[SPARK]
Ouch...
A treasure chest?
[NEESE]
I hear you can find magic items
hidden around dungeons.
Maybe we can use it disembowel
the freakin' beast?
Let's check it out!
Little Dragon, we need
you to distract him
for a while. Now, go!
Well, here it is!
It's a legendary magic item!
[SPARK] Hold it right there,
Black Dragon!
I shall destroy you!
With the legendary magic item...
...the wig of Aphro!
[BLACK DRAGON laughing]
What's so funny?! Come on!
Huh?
[laughter continues]
I... I won...
But why do I feel
so empty inside...?
[DARK ELF, NEESE laugh]
[ALL]
We'll be seeing you!
[SPARK] Suddenly, we are
attacked by an evil storm!
And Neese's body is swept
into its dark power!
Could this be the dark
nightmare she spoke of?!
To save the suffering girl,
we must fight
an invisible enemy!
Next time,
on Record of Lodoss War:
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"Doorway...
The Truth Proclaimed."