[NARRATOR]
Light and darkness...
The final battle of the gods
climaxed in a clash between
Marfa, goddess of all creation,
and Kardis, goddess
of destruction.
At the end of their
fierce battle,
the stricken goddesses
had split the continent,
forming a new land.
Since then, people have come
to call this new continent
"Lodoss - The Accursed Island."
The way that you
embrace me with your
strong and powerful arms
Your haunting words keep me
close to everything about you
Romantic in ways
in ways that almost
tear upon my heart
Can't let you go
Don't you know?
Io sono prigioniera
A captive in
your gentle hands
A prisoner of
your soulful eyes,
your special smile
will never part
If the morning sun
should free me
It really wouldn't let me go
I'd still be caught
inside your love
Can't rise above
the chains of your heart
[bird chirps]
[PARN grunts]
Why not?!
[grunts]
Hey, what's going on
around here?
And why won't you
let us into Alan?
Alan is our royal capital,
and we are under strict orders
not to allow any
strangers into the city,
even if they claim
to be Alanian citizens.
The capital is closed!
Now what is this all about?!
All that I'm
allowed to tell you
is that Alania
will not resist Marmo,
but we will not become
their slaves either!
Ah, which means now they've
decided to sit this one out.
That can't be!
Don't you know
that the Marmo forces
just destroyed
the fortress Myce?
[HEAD GUARD]
An acceptable loss.
[BOTH gasp]
Parn...
Are you telling me
that King Kadomos VII
won't stand up
to the Marmo forces?!
[ETOH, DEEDLIT]
Parn!
Are you?!
[PARN]
Answer me!
[NARRATOR]
News of the invasion by
Emperor Beld of
the dark island of Marmo
soon spread throughout
all of Lodoss.
Alarmed by the swift fall
of the Kingdom of Kannon,
King Fahn of Valis has decided
to dispatch a messenger
to establish an alliance
with the neighboring
Kingdom of Alania.
[FAHN]
Fianna...
This journey will not
be a pleasant one.
But I have no doubt
that you will
successfully
execute your duties
as Princess of Valis.
I promise I will
carry your message
to King Kadomos the VII
without fail, Father.
I hope that we're not too late.
See my daughter-- No, no--
the princess, safely through.
Yes, Your Majesty.
By the honor of
the knights, I swear it.
[groans]
[WAGNARD] Will you not issue the
order to surrender, King Kannon?
[thunder rumbles]
Do so now, and you'll eliminate
any further need for bloodshed.
And who would willingly
deal with devils?!
Kannon's royalty may fall,
but the people of our kingdom
will never submit to you!
I see.
[gasps, groans]
[KARLA]
Well played, my lord.
With this, the east
of Lodoss is yours.
[BELD] Ashram reports
favorably, then?
[KARLA] It's still too early
for such good news.
But fear not.
Despite their numbers,
Alania is no match at all.
[chuckles]
[KARLA] A messenger has been
sent from Valis to Alania.
[BELD] Fahn...
He's making his move.
[KARLA]
I shall attend to this.
She is quite the
cunning woman, is she not?
[BELD grunts]
[BELD] We will use her...
for as long as it's convenient.
[DEEDLIT]
Parn!
Hey!
Hey, how long do you
intend to stay mad, huh?
I'm not angry anymore, okay?
[SLAYN] Are you sure
about that path?
You're heading straight into
the Forest of No Return.
Huh?
--[GHIM grunts]
--Hey, hey, hey!
Wait just a minute.
We're not going
in there, are we?!
Parn...
[PARN] I am! I'll cross
the Forest of No Return,
and I'll get to Valis!
Even if Alania
falls to the Marmo,
I'm sure King Fahn
will stand up to them!
[GHIM] And you're planning on
fighting alongside them.
Hah! You wouldn't even make
a decent gate sentry for them!
No, Ghim!
[WOODCHUCK] Forget it! I'm not
going into that forest!
First of all, you ever heard of
anybody getting out alive?
--Hey!
--You can stay behind,
but I'm gonna be the
first one to make it out!
[WOODCHUCK groans]
Hey!
C'mon, you don't
have to go through
that deathtrap to get there!
We can go around
the forest to get to Valis!
And where are we
supposed to get the time
to take the long way around?
We've got to get
to Valis quickly!
We have to help King Fahn!
[WOODCHUCK groans]
Hey! Somebody, please,
help me out here!
My mind is made up!
Look, I'm not trying
to influence you.
You're free to do
whatever you want.
[DEEDLIT]
Let's go then.
[BOTH]
Huh?!
Let's go right now.
To the Forest of No Return.
But Deedlit...
Ghim, and what about you?
Isn't there something else
you need to do?
Ugh, nevermind
about that right now.
Hold it!
Before we enter, you must
all give your word to me.
Surprise, terror,
anger, anguish...
You must leave these
strong emotions behind,
or else the trees around us
will react in an evil way.
Ugh, I can't believe that
an elf is giving me orders.
[chuckles]
Well, I don't have to
worry about
dwarves like you, Ghim.
You couldn't feel
that much if you tried!
[GHIM grumbles]
"Lord of the forest,
master of plants,
open the sealed door
to the metropolis,
and guide us safely
to the other side."
"Lord of the forest,
master of plants,
open the sealed door
to the metropolis,
and guide us safely
to the other side."
Come on, follow me.
Yeah, right,
like I'm gonna follow her.
[chuckles]
Huh?
Hey, are you guys--
Aw, why me?!
Wait for me!
I don't get it! I'm feelin'
kinda strange inside.
Don't worry about it.
That's what's
supposed to happen.
[DEEDLIT] He's right.
The forest draws out
the reserves
of strength within you.
It's because feelings of
aggression and malice
don't exist here.
[SLAYN] Of course.
The Realm of the Fairies.
Deed, this is
your homeland, isn't it?
[ETOH] I thought
it was lost long ago.
Come on, we can't afford to
waste any more time now!
What's she talking about?
Time behaves differently
in different worlds.
It passes more slowly here.
If we don't leave here soon,
the lapse will inevitably
cause us all to age.
Come along. We'd best
hurry on our way.
You're darn right we should.
The Realm... of the Fairies...
Huh?!
[gasps]
It's my father!
Wait, son! Don't be fooled,
it's only an illusion.
[PARN]
Huh?!
[gasps]
Hey, Parn!
Come on and hurry up!
Or else this place
really will be
the Forest
of No Return for you!
[WOODCHUCK]
Hey! Wait for me!
Huh? Huh?!
Aw! Gold dust!
[laughs]
Huh...?
Wh-What's going on?
[gasps, screams]
--Help me!
--[PARN] Woodchuck!
[WOODCHUCK]
Help! Help! Help!
[groans]
[screams]
"Great spirits of light,
come to me."
You're a fool!
You're falling for
something so obvious!
Calm down, Ghim!
I told you that
the trees and plants
all around here
will react to your anger!
What?
Ghim, no!
[gasps]
[GHIM]
Leylia?!
Leylia!
Huh? Who are you?!
Leylia! Give her back!
[screams]
Hang on, Ghim!
Ghim! Parn!
[BOTH groan]
--[SLAYN] Ghim!
--[ETOH] Parn!
It's okay,
we're both all right!
[bird squaks]
Man, I can't believe we actually
made it outta there alive.
Ghim's journey may be more
difficult than I first thought.
So, what are you
saying, Slayn?
[GHIM]
L-Leylia...
Ghim!
Was the Alanian resistance less
than you expected, Sir Ashram?
Mind your own matters, Karla.
And what have you discovered
about Valis's maneuvers?
Very good. You learned of that
much faster than I expected.
"The smallest pebble that might
impede Emperor Beld's advance,"
isn't that what you said?
You have nothing to fear.
I came only to hear you utter
those exact words to me.
[chuckles]
[ASHRAM groans]
Cursed witch...
[GHIM]
Thanks. I'm all right now.
[ETOH]
Ghim!
Tell me, Ghim. What was it you
thought you saw back there?
[grunts]
Won't you please
tell us, dear friend?
It was Leylia.
L-Leylia?
[PARN] Wait, you don't have to
tell us if you don't want to.
Everyone has secrets they'd
rather keep to themselves.
[DEEDLIT]
You think so?
After all, he's the one who
put us in danger back there.
[PARN]
Deed!
Hmph!
My quest...
My quest is to find Leylia,
the long-lost daughter of Neese,
the High Priestess of Marfa.
Ah, Neese, the legendary
priestess from Tarba.
[GHIM grunts]
Seven years ago, Neese left
the shrine to care for me
after I had been badly hurt
in a mining accident.
Her daughter, Leylia,
concerned about my wounds,
was offering prayers for me.
[screeches]
And where she is now,
we still don't know.
Someone snatched her up.
But Ghim, as the
High Priestess' daughter,
she would have acquired
some skills of her own.
That an ordinary
person would--
--[distant explosions]
--[GROUP gasps]
[WOODCHUCK growls]
[KNIGHT A] The princess!
Protect the princess!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[FIANNA gasps]
Princess Fianna! Fear not!
The Knights of Valis will
defend you with our lives!
[KARLA] Will your prayers
reach the gods?
I wonder.
[FIANNA gasps]
Alania has already
fallen to the Marmo.
[gasps]
[FIANNA]
Somebody, help!
You have nothing
to fear, dear girl.
I have other plans
in mind for you.
I promise not to harm you
in any way, dear child.
Other plans? Like what?
Your sudden disappearance
would probably
cause your father to
move against the Marmo.
[FIANNA gasps]
--[PARN] Huh?
--[KNIGHT B] Princess!
[groans]
--Hey! What was th--
--Look out! That's a fire spell!
[PARN]
Huh?!
[groans]
Hang on!
[KNIGHT C] The princess...
Save Princess Fianna!
Princess Fianna?
You mean the daughter
of King Fahn?
King Fahn of Valis?!
[gasps]
[growls]
Parn, wait! It's too
dangerous to go alone!
Parn, wait!
Hey, this guy takes off
after anything, doesn't he?
[gasps]
"Reveal thy true form and
protect our passage through."
No, Parn, wait.
Hear me, there's terrible
sorcery at work here!
[screams]
[PARN]
Who are you-- [groans]
[SLAYN]
Parn!
Release the princess!
[SLAYN groans]
I've never felt anything
nearly as powerful as this!
How nice. I didn't expect
to find a sorcerer here.
[SLAYN groans]
Only a fool attacks without
first knowing
who his enemy really is.
[PARN groaning]
Why you--!
I said release her.
[groaning]
[panting]
I won't... let you...!
Ha! I won't be beaten!
[KARLA chuckles]
Parn!
That's far enough, young man.
[DEEDLIT gasps]
"Friend Undine,
spirit of water!
Give us your power!"
Why... It can't be!
It's... It's Leylia!
[PARN] You cursed witch!
Let the princess go!
Young boy, because I
respect your courage,
I reward you.
Parn! Is the
princess all right?
[PARN]
Here, take her!
[hollers]
[GROUP gasps]
[BELD laughs]
Alania and Kannon are
no longer threats to me.
Fahn, I haven't forgotten
you these past 30 years.
Next will be your Valis!
[laughing]
What does it matter that
one person should control
when all of us surely
will die over time?
[growls lowly]
[VOICE]
Answer me!
[gasps]
What... can... this be?!
[VOICE]
Answer me!
What is this force
that calls out to me?
Kardis, the dark goddess
in the earth,
can it be?! Kardis!
Let all the wonders
come to me
The fantasy fills,
fills my heart
I'll never wander anymore
For all the love I have,
I have for you
All the spirits of the wind
Spread their magic
wings and fly
Racing at the speed of light
Through the valleys
and the passages of time
When we fell in love
Destiny
Now each night
will have no end
Our nights will never end
Eternity awaits
You and me
Now that you are here
We'll never be alone again
Stay with me, my love