[PEOPLE screaming]
Neese! Neese!
[SOLDIER groans]
Oh, yeah, it's them. The Marmo.
[MARMO A]
This is too easy!
[MARMO laugh]
[MARMO B] Yeah, these Valis
soldiers aren't so tough!
Well, looks like we
got another fight.
We can take care of
these guys, Captain.
You find Neese.
Okay, but be careful!
[ALL yelling]
[NEESE pants]
[NEESE] I have to protect
the Staff of Life! I must!
[FALIS PRIEST groans]
"Great Marfa,
mother of the Earth...
Heal this person's wounds."
Who are you...?
[WAGNARD] So, Doorway... Nice of
you to come. I've been waiting.
[WAGNARD chuckles]
Hmm...?
[WAGNARD]
I see you found yourself
yet another body, Karla.
[KARLA] When you finally succeed
at gathering the two keys
and the Door, what will
you do then, Wagnard?
[WAGNARD]
I owe you no explanation, Karla.
But do not misunderstand
my intentions.
I shall not use my
powers against you.
But why, Kardis?
The goddess of Destruction
is too much for any man.
Why would you want to
resurrect the goddess
whose only intention is
to destroy all of Lodoss?
You gaze at the truth even now.
There is no way that you,
the Grey Witch, cannot be aware
of the enormous power that
lies inside of Lodoss.
The power of the alliance
between Valis and Flaim
now exceeds that of this
dark island of Marmo.
I'm surprised you haven't
broken this alliance up.
Wasn't it you who said you must
destroy all centers of power
so as it prevents
another tragedy
like the Kingdom of Sorcery?
That was why you became
the Grey Witch, wasn't it?
To control the chaos of war
from behind the scenes,
thus insuring a
future for Lodoss?
You believed that by balancing
the powers of Light and Darkness
that you would lead Lodoss to
eternal prosperity, am I right?!
Do you really think that
the resurrection of Kardis
will help achieve that?
[WAGNARD] And what is
that supposed to mean?
[KARLA] Kardis hates the souls
of all living things.
What prosperity could there
possibly be in turning Lodoss
into a wasteland? Or, perhaps...
Perhaps your ultimate
desire is to rule over
a kingdom of ghosts, am I right?
Heh. You may believe
what you want to.
But the truth is,
that if you allow Valis
and Flaim to carry on
as they've been, they will no
longer be following the path
you set for them.
If resurrecting the Destroyer
means destruction of the Light,
then that is Lodoss' fate.
[gasps]
[WAGNARD] Think about
what I've said, Karla.
No one will stand in my way!
When this is over,
I shall reign supreme!
I alone shall be
lord of the dead!
[laughs]
[NEESE pants]
[gasps]
[DARK ELVES cackling]
The Staff of Life!
[DARK ELF A]
Hmm...?
[DARK ELVES] "Tiny spirits
of invisibility...!"
[DARK ELVES squeal]
[gasps]
[DARK ELVES giggle]
Stop! [gasps]
[JAY]
What was that? "Stop"?
I don't think so.
[NEESE]
Huh...?
Unfortunately, I can't
let you go any further.
What are you going to do
with the Staff of Life?!
I don't know. You probably know
much more about it than I do.
Stand aside!
[JAY] This is our duty.
We show no mercy to anyone
who gets in our way.
[NEESE growls, gasps]
[screams]
[NEESE grunts]
[MARMO C]
How 'bout this?!
Too bad, little girl!
Sorry, but play time's over!
[growls]
And now you must die!
[SPARK]
Hold it!
[JAY]
Hmm?
[SPARK pants]
I'm here now!
Are you all right?!
Yes...
[JAY]
Wait... I know you.
You're Spark, aren't you?
I didn't expect to
run into you here.
So that's how you work.
Interesting...
[MARMO D growls]
Neese! I want you
to stay close now!
Kill!
[MARMO yelling]
[PEOPLE screaming]
[GARRACK grunts]
This is no place
to get bogged down in a fight!
[RYNA] True enough, but we can't
just ignore them either!
We're going to have
to end this fast! Ahh!
[ALDO]
"Manna of creation,
become the fires
of destruction!"
[MARMO screaming]
Hey, do you think the
captain is all right?
And Lady Neese?
[swords clashing]
Damn, how could just one guy
be such a giant pain?!
[MARMO E groans]
[gasping]
Now, out of my way.
[growls]
[yells]
[SPARK grunting]
[JAY chuckles]
No, Spark!
Now you die!
[gasps]
[SPARK growls]
[yelling]
[JAY groans]
[sighs]
[whimpering]
[pants]
[BOTH scream]
Neese... Are you all right?
Yes. But I'm afraid
the Staff of Life, it...
You mean, it's been stolen?!
I was trying to go after it,
but then they showed up.
The second key...
No, it can't be...
[grunts]
Wait a minute...
They must be at the port.
They're going to transport
the Staff of Life
out of here on their ship!
If we go after them right now...
I'm going with you.
Too dangerous. You go tell
King Etoh what has happened.
But Spark! Please, wait for--
[gasps]
[groans]
[SPARK gasps]
Neese!
[NEESE gasps, moans]
[screams]
Can it be?! Wangard?!
Come to me, Doorway.
[gasps]
[shrieks]
[SPARK]
Neese!
[shrieking continues]
No! Neese!
[SPARK]
Neese! Neese, snap out of it!
Neese!
[gasps]
[SPARK groans]
[WAGNARD chuckles]
It's hopeless, Doorway.
[SPARK groans]
I can't hold on anymore! Neese!
[SPARK grunts]
[SPARK]
Huh?!
Sorry it took so long
to get here, Captain!
Garrack! Everyone! Help me!
"I call upon the power
of Myrii to grant peace
to this young girl's heart!"
"Manna of all creation!
Please release this holy girl
from this dark covenant!"
Yes!
Hey, guys! It's working!
You won't break my spell again!
[WAGNARD grunts]
[NEESE moans]
[GARRACK, SPARK grunt]
Captain!
Hang on, Garrack!
I'm trying to, but...
but this power's incredible!
[SPARK growls]
It's... It's no use!
If this keeps up,
we're done for!
No! Lady Neese!
Come on! There must be
something we can do!
Please, Neese...
Don't leave me...
Just wake up! Neese!
Just wake up!
Please... Please, open your
eyes! Open your eyes! Neese!
[NEESE groans]
[NEESE]
I got to fight this...
[SPARK]
Neese! Neese! Neese!
Spark, I can...!
What?!
[NEESE groans]
[NEESE]
"Marfa, mother of the Earth!
Drive away this evil light!"
[yells]
Damn you, Neese!
The hole is closing up!
It worked!
It was Lady Neese's iron will
that drove this evil magic away!
So this... this is
the power of Marfa...
Hey, we did it!
Neese, we brought you back.
[sighs]
[LEAF, RYNA]
Spark!
[ALDO]
Lady Neese!
Damn! That's two
times I've tried,
and two times I've failed!
But I swear to you, our struggle
isn't over... Not yet...
"I summon the power
of Myrii, the War God.
Heal this brave youth's wounds."
[SPARK groans]
[ALL sigh]
Priest Greevus... It's you...
Ah... You will be all right now.
Everyone... [gasps]
Where's Neese?!
How are you?
Fine, thanks to you, my friend.
Huh?
I never could've escaped
without your help.
I thought for sure the dark
wizard was going to capture me.
But I heard your voice
calling me and I came back.
It was you who pulled Neese back
from that nightmare, Spark.
So please accept
my thanks, Spark.
There's no need to thank me.
What I did is what a knight
is supposed to do anyway.
--Ohh...
--[RYNA giggles]
So, what's our next move,
Captain I'm-Almost-A-Knight?
Those Dark Elves got away
with the Staff of Life.
And that is why I
must go to Marmo.
[BOTH]
Huh?
The two keys must be reclaimed.
And I must settle things
with the dark wizard
once and for all.
She wants to settle with him?
Captain, did you hear?
Yes, I heard. And I'm going.
[GARRACK]
Wha--?!
Isn't that too dangerous?
But King Kashue's already
ordered us to return to Flaim.
If you disobey him like this,
you'll never get to
be a knight, Spark.
I know, but I've
made up my mind.
I'm ready to go to Marmo
right now. For Neese.
Someone must go with her
to make sure she's safe.
And there's another thing.
I think saving Lodoss
is more important
than following orders.
Well, Spark, now you
know who you are.
[LEAF giggles]
That's right.
What're we worried about?
We're not soldiers,
not knights, not anything.
All we really have to do
is protect each other.
Eh? Right, Garrack?
[GARRACK]
Yeah, sure. Whatever you say.
[LEAF]
And Aldo's coming too, right?
Thank you.
Everyone...
[ETOH]
I see.
And there's no talking you
out of this, is there?
I also agree that it would
be dangerous to try this
with a large group.
Besides, without close
friends to rely on,
you'd never be able to make
it through such a challenge.
Yes.
And will you be
leaving immediately?
Yes. As soon as we
can find a ship.
In that case, you may
travel as far as Kanon
aboard one of our
military ships.
May the gods of Light watch
over and protect you.
[ETOH] Seven brave lights now
set out for the dark island.
It seems the time has come for
me to make a decision as well.
A decision as king.
For the good of Valis...
and all of Lodoss.
[SPARK] What Parn told me
is starting to ring true.
[PARN] Don't become a man
who lives only for the duty
that's given to him.
[SPARK] It's my decision
to make this journey.
I swear I'll recover
the two keys, and also...
Is something wrong, Spark?
Neese... I swear that
I will protect you.
Thanks.
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've
all been waiting for,
the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
Hey, Spark! Hey, Spark!
The freakin' dope is lost again.
Ah?! Oh, how cute!
Hello, little rodent--uh,
squirrel!
[SPARK]
Hey, Neese! Help me! Neese!
It's no use, dammit!
What a lousy break!
First of all, why the hell
is there a hole here
in the first place?!
For your information there,
I dug this hole.
Hah.
Don't be so proud!
I didn't fall down here
'cause I wanted to!
I fell for this, cookie-head.
Give me Mama Dragon's note!
Not so fast!
Why not?!
Because, the secret of Neese's
cookies is in here.
[SPARK] Give it back!
Give it back! Give it back!
[DARK ELF A]
No, hey! No!
It's written in Dragon!
Stifle, will ya, kid?
[BOTH grunting, groaning]
No use. We'll never get up.
I thought you knights
were all so smart.
Oh, get real!
Besides, you can just fly
out of here, can't you?!
Hey, you're right there,
cookie-head.
Whoopty-doo!
I'll be seein' youse!
Hey, come back!
Hey-hey-hey, ha!
Ouch there!
--Ah!
--[DARK ELF groans]
Li'l Dragon!
[LITTLE DRAGON squawks]
[SPARK]
You saved me, Little Dragon!
By the way, what did
that letter say?
It said to be careful
on your trip.
That's it?! Hah!
Funny thing is, I feel
like I forgot something...
I'll never give up
there, little girl!
I'll get those cookies!
[NEESE, SPARK]
We'll be seein' you!
[SPARK]
With new resolve in our hearts,
we set out on our journey.
Can we make it safely through
Kanon and find our way
to the dark island?
We race through a forest
and are confronted by
terrible monsters
and Marmo mercenaries.
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War :
Chronicles of
the Heroic Knight :
"Reunion...
In a Distant War-Torn Land."