Wait! Oh, Shiris, please wait!
Shiris! Shiris!
[SHIRIS] Oh... Would you
quit your whining, Orson?!
[ORSON]
Huh?!
[SHIRIS]
It's hard for everyone!
Can't you just shut up and
walk like the rest of us?!
[ORSON]
Huh.
Why don't we rest?
But sir...
I think we're finally within
striking distance of Ashram.
Besides, a forced march like
this is a drain on everyone.
Even if we caught
up with Ashram,
there'd be no way
we could beat him
given the condition we're in.
You're right. Listen up!
We'll stop here and
rest for a while.
[ORSON sighs]
Say, Parn.
[PARN]
Huh?
Orson...
Why do you think his
emotions came back so fast?
I don't know.
But I think I prefer the
old Orson to the new one.
He's been living without
feelings for so long.
I think Orson's gonna
have some trouble
learning how to deal with them.
Is that why?! Shiris!
[SHIRIS] Ugh, Parn! Can you do
something about this guy?!
At this rate,
he'll never be able to fight!
But Parn, I--
I'm too frightened to fight.
Then why did you even
bother to come along?
Because I love you!
[gasps]
Wh-What did you
just say, Orson?!
I mean it.
Ever since the spirit of anger
was released from my heart,
I realized that deep down,
I was in love with
you all along, Shiris.
And for once,
I'll be able to show you.
[SHIRIS]
Uh--
[sighs]
Hey, Orson, won't you tell us?
How did your feelings just
suddenly come back?
I think-- Here's what
happened to me.
I was fighting against
Ashram when he cut my arm
with the demon sword,
Soul Crusher.
I felt its power begin to
flow through my body.
Then when I heard Abram's
roar on Blue Dragon Island,
the spirit's control over
my heart got even weaker.
Then... Well,
ever since that time,
I've been more able to
resist the spirit's control.
It makes sense.
Ashram's demon sword
and Abram's dragon roar
have a direct effect over
possessive spirits like Hyuri.
But what sort of effect are
you talking about, Deed?
Has the spirit of anger
fled his heart?
No, I can still feel him.
But he's definitely lost the
power to control my heart.
You should all listen up.
The spirit of anger exists in
the heart of every human being.
But as long as you can
restrain it with reason,
you can live with your
anger and still be happy.
Orson, I'm really glad you've
got your feelings back and all,
but you've got to understand,
the one I'm in love
with... is him!
[PARN]
Uh-- Uh--
[gasps] Hey!
Shiris, that's not really true.
You were angry with Parn
because there was no way
you could beat him,
so you replaced the anger
by fooling yourself
into believing
that you love him.
[growls]
You reacted just
like a little girl
when you lost the fight
with Ashram's lady warrior.
But you think it's okay
to lose to a man,
just as long as you're
in love with him.
Well, Shiris, you really
can't have it both ways.
[SHIRIS]
Shut up!
Getting your feelings back
doesn't mean you know
anything about me.
Give me a break!
I am honestly and
truly in love with Parn!
And it has nothing to do with
losing to that Amazon before!
You don't have any insight
into people's hearts,
so just shut up!
I'm... I'm sorry.
We have arrived.
This is definitely the way
into Shooting Star's volcano.
Let's go.
Please wait a moment,
Sir Ashram.
What now?
You can see it for
yourself, Sir Ashram.
Shooting Star leaves his nest to
hunt for many days at a time.
If we wait until
Shooting Star leaves,
we can simply walk in and
get the Scepter of Domination
without a struggle.
He's right. It's suicide to
fight a fully-active dragon.
And there's nothing righteous
about fighting
unnecessary battles.
Somehow, I doubt it will work.
Groder, Smeddy, stand guard.
[GRODER, SMEDDY]
Yes, sir.
The rest of us will wait for
the beast to leave his nest.
Is that clear?
[roaring]
[gasps]
What's wrong?
[DEEDLIT]
Look!
[PARN]
It's Shooting Star!
[CECIL] Oh no!
He's headed for Raiden again!
[MAAR]
Hm?
Hey! Look!
They're here.
I'll get her now.
Some troops from Flaim?
We've got to fight them!
No, sir!
Shooting Star has finally
left his lair to go hunt.
We may never get another
chance like this.
Groder...
We'll hold them off.
And you must go inside
with Priest Hobb.
Get the Scepter of Domination
and become king of Lodoss
once and for all!
Heh...
You have a way
with words, Groder.
Very well, I'll leave it to you.
[ALL]
Sir!
[PARN]
Over there! It's them!
Looks like they don't want
us to go any further.
That's fine with me!
It looks like the little girl
and her friends have come back.
But there are a few
new ones with them.
[GRODER growls]
[GRODER]
It's that grass runner.
Watch me now, Orson.
I'll show you and everybody else
that I can beat that
woman warrior.
But Shiris!
You're still tired from your
trek through the mountains!
Maybe you should rest first.
I'll be fine.
I'm gonna settle this
with her in no time flat.
But... you'll die!
[PARN] Something's wrong.
I don't see Ashram.
That must mean he's--
[GRODER]
Ashram's destiny must prevail.
Now go. Protect us from them!
Look at them!
Highness, Ashram's
not with them!
I know. He must be
inside the volcano.
With Shooting Star
away from his nest,
even a child could
grab the scepter.
[PARN]
Then there's no time to waste.
You go in, sir.
Leave this to me.
Right, Parn.
All right now, let's go!
[PARN yelling]
Stop that man!
[yells]
Damn! He's in!
"I summon thee, Falaris,
God of Darkness!
Grant unto me your strength
and paralyze this adversary
with the spell of stone!"
"Great Marfa!
Return this man's heart and
body to the way they were."
So, that one is a
priestess of Marfa.
[yelps]
It's an earthquake!
[yells]
Oh no! It's a behemoth!
That's the strongest
land spirit there is!
"I summon thee, Iruku,
great king of the wind!"
Let's go, everyone!
[swords clanging]
They just keep coming...
[yells]
Where is that woman?
I figured she'd come
right after me.
Please don't fight her.
Shiris, don't!
Just shut up!
[gasps]
Look out, Shiris!
Orson...
And so we meet again.
I really didn't expect to see
you again, my little girl.
Do you really wanna take me on?
[SHIRIS]
I was careless with you before.
But I won't be this time!
Not careless. Hah, you just
weren't strong enough.
Shut up, you!
Hold on, Shiris!
[ASTAR]
That elf!
I didn't think she'd be able to
summon the king of the wind!
If two spirits this
powerful clash,
it would be catastrophic!
[DEEDLIT] If you send your
behemoth to attack us,
Iruku will cut you down.
So don't dare move.
I should have studied...
swordsmanship...
...for situations like this.
I didn't think anyone could
conjure such a fire spell.
What?!
[yells]
I can't let myself
be killed here! Not now!
[yells]
"Endless darkness,
cover me in your shadows
and transport me
from this place."
What? He ran away!
Are you all right?
I was so wrong, Cecil.
You never should have
been a sorcerer.
You are far too
good as a warrior.
[CECIL chuckles]
[SMEDDY]
What's the matter, little girl?
You're a lot clumsier
than you were before.
[growls] Shut up!
[SHIRIS groans]
I'm not gonna let you beat me!
[SMEDDY] Come on, what
happened to all that spirit?!
"God of Darkness! Descend
thy cloak upon the enemy!"
"Marfa, mother of the Earth,
great protector of all who love
life, repel the darkness!"
Huh?! The power of her
faith broke my spell!
[gasps]
[yells]
[GABERRA]
Now you die!
What--?!
"Marfa, I deliver another soul
to receive your guidance!"
[groaning]
"God of Darkness!
Bring evil upon her soul!
Turn her words of love
into words of hatred,
her comfort into torture..."
"Marfa, grant peace to
this poor man's soul..."
[SHIRIS screams]
Shiris!
Out of my way! Dammit!
Ugh... Orson...
What should I do?!
What should I do?
[ORSON]
No! No! Damn it all!
Why can't I protect
the woman I love?
Don't I have the
strength to save her?!
Ah! I know you! You're the
spirit of anger, Hyuri.
Hyuri, please give me
the strength I need!
Give me the strength
I need to save Shiris!
Oh, please, Hyuri. Turn me
into a berserker once again.
I can't lose her.
I can't stand by and let
another person I love die.
If I can't save her, I don't
care what happens to me!
Please, Hyuri, give me the
strength one last time.
[ORSON groaning]
[growling]
[DEMON snickers]
So it's over, little girl.
You're through.
Orson... I'm sorry.
It looks-- It looks like
you were right, after all.
[gasps] No, Orson...
What the--?!
Idiot... You were finally...
finally cured...
Ah! Damn you!
Orson...
[roaring]
Oh... no...!
[SHIRIS]
Orson...
Strike me down, Orson.
You're going to die,
and it's all my fault.
That's right, now we
can die together.
Shiris!
[SLAYN]
Shiris, don't!
Now. Kill me now. Go ahead.
It's not true... Orson...
Say it isn't so.
We were... We were always
supposed to be together!
Please, Orson!
Answer me, please!
[SHIRIS]
Orson... Orson...
Orson!
--Welcome...
--...to Lodoss Island!
What you've all been
waiting for...
...the second part!
[giggles]
[KASHUE]
Hm? Hm? Hm?
Hey, come on! Where are we?
There's no doubt about it,
we're totally lost!
How did we ever get
inside this cavern?
Huh?! Did I say "cavern"?
Tell me, what's a "cav earn"?
Depends on what a cav's worth!
Your skills have
grown again, Parn!
I'm so proud.
Thank you very much,
Your Highness!
[BOTH] What do you two
think you're doing?!
[BOTH scream]
This really stinks!
At this rate, we'll
never get out of here!
But according to the information
we bought back in town,
the Scepter of Domination
should be down here somewhere!
[SHIRIS] There's no way
that scepter is down here.
Face it, those guys back
in town got over on you.
They saw you coming.
Uh... Hey! What's that?
[SHIRIS yelps]
[SHIRIS]
Don't scare me like that again.
What is this thing?
It looks like a treasure chest
with some sort of writing on it.
Must you always pop
in like that?!
It looks like some
ancient language...
Tell me, what does it say?
Well, parts of it are
worn away, but um, uh...
..."da"... "ee"... "er"...
"oh"... ..."uh"... "mm"...
...something... "shun"?
"A terrible condition"?
"A kingly proclomation"?
"The director needs a vacation"?
[ALL]
"The Scepter of Domination!"
That's it! We finally found it!
Hey, let's check it out!
[ALL]
Huh?
[DEEDLIT]
Ah! This thing is a coffin!
[SHIRIS]
I miss my mummy!
Oh well, it looks like this
case is all wrapped up.
Wait, Slayn!
I think I've got it!
It's a special on mummification!
That's gotta be it!
[ALL yelp]
[ALL]
We'll be seeing you!
[PARN]
Fire Dragon Mountain,
site of the impending showdown!
It is here that our
final battle begins!
Ashram's demon sword
screams out against
King Kashue and Shooting
Star, the fire dragon.
Who will win this fierce battle?
The future of Lodoss will
be decided by the victor.
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War:
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"The Scepter of Domination...
The Dream of a United Lodoss."