[SPARK pants]
[panting]
[SPARK]
Neese!
[SPARK gasps]
[yells]
[chuckles]
The power... This is the power
of Kardis the Destroyer!
And now, I shall rule the dead!
Magnificent! Magnificent!
[laughs]
Neese!
No, Neese!
Wagnard!
[chuckles]
It seems you're too late.
There's nothing you can do now.
The resurrection
ceremony is over.
The time has come
for me to become lord
of the kingdom of death!
Slayn, what does he mean?
The forbidden spells
that Wagnard stole
gave him the powers
of eternal sorcery.
It is the ultimate gift
of the Destroyer's power.
If Kardis the Destroyer
is allowed to be released
into the world,
then everyone will die!
[SPARK]
That's what this is all about?!
If Wagnard should get his way,
he will turn Lodoss
into a land of the dead and
rule forever as its king.
[WAGNARD laughs]
[groans]
And once I become king,
I will finally be released
from the pain of
Ralkas' punishment!
All that's left is to open
the body of the Doorway
and Kardis shall
finally be reborn!
[laughs]
Karla!
"Ladeera ladeera
vanna ve Kardis."
[KARLA, WAGNARD]
"Vanna dol gel ru deldo vir..."
"Ladeera vanna dol...
Ludeera aldee dees."
[screams]
Neese!
The spell is getting stronger.
The Destroyer's being reborn!
The Doorway!
[NEESE sobs]
[SLAYN]
The Doorway... It's opening!
Karla, stop it!
[SPARK growls]
I won't let you!
[GARRACK]
Captain!
[GREEVUS]
Go, Garrack!
Master Slayn, Leylia,
you two go after Karla.
Aldo, keep your
guard up and cover them.
[SPARK yells]
Ha, ha! Don't waste your time.
"Holy spirits of water,
become a shield
and destroy the dark fire!"
[gasps]
[SPARK groans]
It can't be!
[groaning]
I won't... I won't let you!
I will not let you interfere!
"Mist of agony that steals life!
Obey my will and
let darkness fall!"
[SPIRIT hisses]
No, not that spell...
Spark, look out!
[SPARK yells]
[GARRACK]
Look out!
[GARRACK groans]
Captain, you got to look sharp!
If you get caught
up in that mist,
Wagnard's magic will take you!
Yeah, but...!
The Mist of Agony will put
a victim into eternal sleep.
If that stuff hits you, it'll
steal your life away in no time.
Can't you cast a
protection spell?
Ryna, we are in the
temple of the Destroyer.
Myrii's power will
not work here.
Damn, we can't even move!
I know! But what about Neese?
[KARLA] "Ladeera vanna dol.
Ladeera rui deer."
[LEYLIA]
Karla!
[NANEEL groans]
[LEYLIA]
Why...? Why are you doing this?
I know you think your
actions are justified,
but can any good come of this?
Oh, no... I thought you
hated dark sorcery.
So why, Karla? The people of
Kastuul destroyed themselves
because they frogot their
limits, but Kardis' resurrection
will kill everyone on Lodoss!
Surely you must understand
what that means!
To me, it's not a question
as to whether the power
is good or evil.
[gasps]
[KARLA] A great power must be
balanced by another great power.
It is the only way to ensure
a lasting peace for Lodoss.
Karla, if you keep this up...
...I swear that I will...
Kill me?
Very well. But remember that
the moment your blade
pierces my breast, my mind will
take complete control over you.
Would you like to
open the Doorway
with your own hands, Leylia?
Lady Leylia...
Karla's true form is
in the golden circlet.
It allows her to completely
posess the body
of anyone who touches
it or who kills her.
You mean...
[SLAYN] Yes, she can
move from body to body.
She can even select her hosts.
As long as Karla still exists--
Are you saying, Master Slayn,
that there's nothing we can do?
We must not kill her, Aldonova.
All we can try to do is get
that circlet off her head.
[KARLA] The turning gears of
fate cannot be stopped now.
This is the destiny of Lodoss.
You cannot interfere.
[gasping]
"Ladeera vanna dol..."
Karla!
[KARLA] "Ladeera rui deer...
Ladeera vanna dol..."
This is the day!
This is the day I've dreamed
of for so very long!
Now let the world be quiet
and listen to the final spell!
"Ahre di gelra Kardis!
Ledooran zan engrool!
Ladeera ve Kardis!
Ladeera vanna dol!
Ludeera alri dees..."
Why, that...
that son of a bitch!
If we don't act now,
he'll complete the spell.
What should we do?! Captain!
Garrack...
[GARRACK]
Huh?
On the count of three,
I'm going to rush him.
You stay behind me and
kill the dark wizard
as soon as you see him!
Stay behind you...?
Captain, what do you
think you're gonna do?
Spark...
It's not safe! You can't!
[SPARK] Greevus, we've got
no other options now.
I swore...
I swore I'd save Neese even
if it cost me my life.
So, please...
But Captain...
Obey.
On the count of three, right?
Let's go!
Ready when you are!
All right...
One...
[SPARK]
Two...
Three!
--[SPARK] Huh?!
--[GARRACK yells]
Garrack!
[GARRACK yells]
[SPARK]
Garrack!
[yelling continues]
[WAGNARD]
Huh?
[yells]
Die!
[laughs]
"Mist of agony that steals life,
obey my will and let
darkness fall!"
[GARRACK whimpers]
[WAGNARD chuckles]
Wagnard!
[gasps]
[yells]
[WAGNARD screams]
[screaming continues]
No! This can't be happening!
I was... I was so close to it!
[screams]
[sobbing]
[DEEDLIT]
"Mighty spirits of flame.
Engulf this cursed
person in hell fire!"
[SLAYN]
Deedlit!
"Block the witch's
evil spell! Now!"
[KARLA grunts]
[KARLA]
"Ladeera vanna dol..."
We can't let her
finish that spell!
[KARLA]
"Ladeera rui deer..."
That's enough, Karla! Yah!
"...ve Kardis..."
Hang on, Neese!
You'll die! Die!
[yells]
You're coming with me!
I won't die alone!
[screams]
[SPARK]
Neese!
[SPARK grunts]
Neese! Neese!
[NEESE groans]
Oh, Neese...
[RYNA]
Garrack! No!
[SPARK gasps]
Oh, Garrack...
Spark told him to stay behind,
so why did he...?
Garrack was only following
King Kashue's orders.
He had only one mission:
to protect Spark's life.
[gasps]
Garrack was really a nobleman
in the royal court of Flaim.
King Kashue personally
selected him.
Since Spark is in
line to be king,
Garrack had
no other choice!
When Spark said that
he'd be the decoy,
Garrack knew there would
be no way to stop him,
so he sacrificed
himself instead.
Funny, isn't it?
He'd call himself a mercenary,
but in the end,
he was more valiant and selfless
than the bravest knight.
[LEAF whimpers]
"O great God of War, Myrii...
Grant eternal peace to this
brave warrior's soul..."
Garrack...
[gasps]
It's over now, my husband,
isn't it?
[NEESE groans]
Oh, Spark...
Oh, Neese...
You're safe. It's over now.
[gasps]
"...ve Kardis..."
[screams]
[gasps]
[gasping]
What's happening?!
[SPARK groans]
Neese!
Oh, no...
At last, the resurrection
ceremony is complete.
I am now reborn upon
the land of Lodoss!
[SPARK whimpers]
[gasping]
What the hell is going on?
[SPIRITS hissing]
[yelling]
What was that?!
To the ground, men!
Everybody land!
[TROLLS growling]
[NANEEL] The living are fated
to return to nothingness.
It is the ultimate
fate of all light
to be consumed by darkness.
Huh...? [gasps]
[gasping]
[NANEEL] My long slumber
is now at its end.
I shall lead this accursed
land into eternal darkness.
To regain the history once lost,
the Doorway has been opened!
That's... Kardis!
It can't be! That means
we're too late!
But what shall become of
Lodoss and Lady Neese?
Oh, dear... It's really over...
No way! No! You can't
do this! Neese!
[NANEEL chuckles]
[NEESE]
Spark! Spark!
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've
all been waiting for,
the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
[LITTLE DRAGON squawking]
Boy, Little Dragon
sure is happy.
He's so happy because he's going
to see the mama
dragon real soon.
[VOICE]
Oh, I'm so happy, dear!
It's my little baby dragon!
I've missed you so much!
Come to mama, my baby!
[SPARK]
Who is that?
It's Mama Dragon!
Mama!
Well, now that
we're together again,
what do you say we take a walk
in the sky together, huh?
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Mama, ma!
She was so worried;
she came out to meet him!
Motherly love's so
freakin' beautiful.
Mama's right over here.
Ugh, that wasn't a bad
impression there, huh?
Look out! It's the Dark Elf!
I can't believe you freakin'
tricked us again!
Hey, hon,
now that I've taken care of
that little flamethrower,
gettin' those cookies from you
should be as easy as pie!
Now stand still while
I cast my spell! Yah!
"Whoopty-doo, whoopty-doo, there
little boy, there little girl!
Hah, whoopty-doo!"
[BOTH scream]
[DARK ELF]
I'll take that there, huh.
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ma!
Hey, ha, I got them cookies!
[DARK ELF] And now I can return
them to Ashram, the dark baker!
Huh?
[DARK ELF]
Ouch, huh...
[SPARK]
Now that's divine intervention!
Just your typical bust of faith!
[squawks]
Oh, look! It's freakin'
Big Dragon Mountain!
Now we really will meet
the mama dragon!
[squawking]
Which means that I'll
be a knight any day now!
Great, Spark!
Oh, man... Ashram's
gonna kill me again...
[DARK ELF]
We'll be seein' youse!
[SPARK] The terrible darkness
moves across the land.
Are we really too late
to stop the Destroyer?!
Neese! Try to remember
who you really are!
[NEESE] "Marfa, great
mother of the Earth...
Bring light to this
accursed land."
I want to go back
to be with Spark.
[SPARK] Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War :
Chronicles of the
Heroic Knight :
"Hero...
The Birth of a New Knight."