[NARRATOR]
Light and darkness...
The final battle of the gods
climaxed in a clash between
Marfa, goddess of all creation,
and Kardis, goddess
of destruction.
At the end of their
fierce battle,
the stricken goddesses
had split the continent,
forming a new land.
Since then, people have come
to call this new continent
"Lodoss - The Accursed Island."
The way that you
embrace me with your
strong and powerful arms
Your haunting words keep me
close to everything about you
Romantic in ways
in ways that almost
tear upon my heart
Can't let you go
Don't you know?
Io sono prigioniera
A captive in
your gentle hands
A prisoner of
your soulful eyes,
your special smile
will never part
If the morning sun
should free me
It really wouldn't let me go
I'd still be caught
inside your love
Can't rise above
the chains of your heart
[NARRATOR] The war between Beld,
the dark emperor of Marmo,
and King Fahn of Valis,
has shaken all of Lodoss.
It ended in the deaths
of both leaders.
In generations to come,
this battle will be known
as "The War of Heroes."
But few will know of the
mysterious, shadowy forces
that were at work
behind the scenes.
Is that for Leylia?
It is.
I think she'd expect something
a bit fancier, don't you?
Listen to me.
This is a gift for Leylia.
The woman you've seen so far
is a witch named Karla.
[SHIRIS] Boy,
that really burns me up!
The mayor practically begged us
to protect his village!
Hey, doesn't that
make you mad?! Orson!
What is it with you?!
The war ends and
they just boot us out
like we were
some sort of enemy!
What do they think
mercenaries are for?!
[horse hooves approaching]
Where do you think
they're from?
Huh, I don't know.
One of them looks
like a mercenary.
The other's a thief, I think...
And... an elf?
An elf. Marmo?
It could be. Hmm...
And they're headed
straight for the village.
It's not our problem anymore.
That's not the point, Orson!
[NARRATOR] Hoping to win the
lasting peace for Lodoss,
Parn and his friends race
toward Karla's castle.
[yells]
[gasps]
[horse whinnies]
[BOTH scream]
Hey! What's goin' on?!
[PARN]
Etoh! Wood!
[SHIRIS]
Orson! Take care of them!
Huh?!
[SHIRIS]
Yaaah!
[PARN grunts]
Parn!
Marmo soldiers?!
Who's a Marmo?!
Ah! So, you can't win
without your little elf
helping you, huh?!
Back off, Deed!
Everything's okay.
I think we just have a little
misunderstanding here.
This is a little violent for a
simple misunderstanding, no?
[yells]
[grunts]
Come on!
I told you that
we're not Marmo!
Then what's
that elf doing here?!
What's with you?
Don't tell me that you can't
tell the difference
between me and a Dark Elf.
What?!
[yells]
[grunts]
[WOODCHUCK growls]
Whoa!
[crackling]
And how many priests
of Falis do you see
with Marmo soldiers, huh?
[gasps]
We're truly sorry about this,
but we're in a hurry
and we have to leave.
[SHIRIS]
Oh...
[ORSON yells]
What's going on?!
Drop your sword! Right now!
--[PARN] What?!
--[SHIRIS] Hurry!
Huh?!
[snarls]
[yells]
Ahh!
Parn!
Orson, no! Stop it! Calm down!
[ORSON growls]
[gasps]
[PARN grunting]
Hey, what's with this guy?
Look, no one can make him
stop once Orson gets mad.
That's why I told you
to drop your sword!
And you expected me
to listen to you?
--Parn!
--Etoh, wait!
I think he's a...
a berserker!
[yells]
Huh...?
Orson, stop it! I'm all right!
And the village is all right,
too! No one has to die!
Just calm down!
Just listen to me!
[growling]
No!
Let him go!
I'm sorry we thought
you were Marmo.
I'll help you anyway I can,
just don't kill him.
[gasps]
This poor, tortured
soul is my friend.
[sighs]
Parn. We'd better
be on our way.
We don't have time to get
involved with a berserker.
A berserker?
[DEEDLIT] He's been
possessed by Hyuri,
the spirit of rage and madness.
He's completely lost
any fear of death.
[WOODCHUCK]
Hmm...
[DEEDLIT] Yes. It is said
when a berserker passes,
only corpses remain.
--[SLAYN] Ghim.
--[GHIM] Enough waiting!
But Ghim, how do you
intend to release Leylia
from the power of the witch?
[GHIM] Leylia will know me.
I know she will.
Now, Slayn, if you try
any of your trickery
on me again, I'll...
[SLAYN]
Huh?
Ghim!
Let me do this alone, Slayn.
[door creaks]
[KARLA] I was
looking forward to this,
and only the dwarf shows up.
[GHIM growls]
Karla! It's not you...
You are Leylia!
You are the daughter of Neese,
priestess of Marfa!
Remember! Leylia!
[KARLA]
Did I not tell you?
Her consciousness no longer
exists. Only I remain.
[GHIM growls]
[KARLA chuckles]
[KARLA]
You cannot harm me.
This is your
beloved Leylia's body.
[GHIM growls]
[GHIM sighs]
[KARLA] Valiant, good dwarf.
But I am not so forgiving.
[gasps]
Huh?
You're just in time.
[yells, grunts]
[GHIM] If... you...
want a body...
[groans]
...take mine... instead!
You surely think
too highly of yourself.
[yells]
[KARLA]
Hmm?
Ghim!
Tell me why! Why did you
have to kill Beld, Karla?!
[KARLA] Oh. Would you
have preferred it
if Beld conquered Lodoss?
[PARN]
What?!
[KARLA] Do you really think I
would've given Lodoss to him?
Or anyone else, for that matter.
But what gives you the right?
[KARLA]
Had Fahn survived,
the outcome would
have been the same.
All was done to save
Lodoss from destruction.
All so Lodoss
could survive forever.
Liar!
It's no lie.
I love Lodoss, as you do.
You think I'd believe you?!
[yells]
[grunts]
Parn!
[PARN screams]
[WOODCHUCK groaning]
[PARN gasps]
Wood!
Hah!
[SLAYN grunting]
[groans]
Ah! Slayn!
[yells]
Parn, no!
[PARN yelling]
[grunts]
Parn!
[groaning]
[PARN]
Huh?
Ah!
[KARLA]
Look well upon this.
The destruction of Kastuul,
glorious Kingdom of Sorcery.
The Kingdom of Sorcery...
What... What do you mean?
[KARLA] Endless battles
to recover the power
of total domination.
Such is the torment of Lodoss.
The destruction
of Kastuul, my homeland,
left me with one lesson:
power must never again
be allowed to settle
in just one place.
As long as
it remains scattered,
the destruction
will never be complete.
And so I cause these wars.
Yes, for the past
five centuries,
I have thus protected Lodoss.
No, it... It can't be...
[KARLA chuckles]
[KARLA] It's still
not too late for you.
Will you not come along
and guide the future
of Lodoss with me?
Come. Throw off
your old armor
and take up
a new mantle to wear.
[gasps]
I... No...
No, I don't believe you...
Someone who
truly protects Lodoss
wouldn't do it by playing
with other people's lives.
We're not just pawns
in your sick chess game!
[grunts, yells]
[grunting]
[DEEDLIT]
Parn!
Are you all right?!
[PARN groans]
That witch is gonna
kill every one of us
before we can get that
circlet off of her forehead.
Circlet?!
You mean that thing--?!
Yes, Ghim. Wort told us that
the circlet on her forehead
is Karla's true form.
[GHIM]
Hmm...
Leylia!
[KARLA] It would seem
I misjudged you.
I have no use for pawns
who refuse to be moved.
[KARLA grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[GHIM growls]
Look out, Ghim!
--Ghim!
--No, Parn!
You haven't got
a chance out there!
But...!
[growling]
[ALL gasp]
[growling continues]
You... are... Leylia...!
What... What are you?
Hear me... Remember....
You are Leylia!
That's who you are!
Ah! Come on! We gotta
do something to help him!
Parn! Now's our chance!
[PARN yells]
[WOODCHUCK growls]
[yells]
[PARN yells]
[DEEDLIT screams]
[groans]
[KARLA screams]
[screaming continues]
Leylia...
No! Ghim!
[ETOH gasps]
[gasps]
Speak to me! Ghim!
No...!
[WOODCHUCK]
Huh...?
No... No!
No...!
Ghim finally won
the victory he sought.
Surely he had no regrets.
Ghim...
Uh...
[sniffling]
Woodchuck.
[NARRATOR] There is no
stopping the passage of time.
But no sooner
does one realize this,
than a new chapter begins.
Let all the wonders
come to me
The fantasy fills,
fills my heart
I'll never wander anymore
For all the love I have,
I have for you
All the spirits of the wind
Spread their magic
wings and fly
Racing at the speed of light
Through the valleys
and the passages of time
When we fell in love
Destiny
Now each night
will have no end
Our nights will never end
Eternity awaits
You and me
Now that you are here
We'll never be alone again
Stay with me, my love