[NARRATOR]
Light and darkness...
The final battle of the gods
climaxed in a clash between
Marfa, goddess of all creation,
and Kardis, goddess
of destruction.
At the end of their
fierce battle,
the stricken goddesses
had split the continent,
forming a new land.
Since then, people have come
to call this new continent
"Lodoss - The Accursed Island."
The way that you
embrace me with your
strong and powerful arms
Your haunting words keep me
close to everything about you
Romantic in ways
in ways that almost
tear upon my heart
Can't let you go
Don't you know?
Io sono prigioniera
A captive in
your gentle hands
A prisoner of
your soulful eyes,
your special smile
will never part
If the morning sun
should free me
It really wouldn't let me go
I'd still be caught
inside your love
Can't rise above
the chains of your heart
[NARRATOR] The narrow
victory in the seemingly
hopeless battle with
the demon dragon,
Shooting Star,
created a joyous uproar
in Flaim's royal
castle of Akrohd.
And news of the safe
return of King Kashue,
who had been
given up for dead,
was cause enough for the
battle-weary soldiers to forget,
for a moment, the ominous
events brewing in Marmo.
[doorknob clicks]
[DEEDLIT]
Parn?
[gasps]
[PARN]
Uh, sorry I woke you.
[chuckles]
It's all right.
Oh...
[DEEDLIT]
Mm...
--[DEEDLIT] What's wrong?
--Huh?
Ah...
[chuckles nervously]
N-Nothing...
--[DEEDLIT] Parn?
--[PARN] Huh?
Thanks a lot.
Ah... Uh...
Sure.
[DEEDLIT chuckles]
You were with him,
weren't you?
What's wrong?
That's what I hate
about you, Orson.
I thought by now you'd know
what not to ask me.
After all, how many years
have we been together?
[KASHUE]
Marmo?
Aye. With Ashram dead,
we just assumed that Marmo
would revert to the dark
island it used to be, but...
[KASHUE]
Hmm?
How can I describe it?
It's as if all of Marmo
bristles with some new force.
What?
Sometimes the earth
shakes and growls
like some great and evil beast.
And even the creatures
who live there
seem to be tormented and afraid.
Afraid?
Of what?
[KASHUE]
Mmm.
[bird screeching]
[distant howling]
[screeching continues]
[grunts]
Huh? I'm alive.
[VOICE] Is a man's path really
of his own choosing?
Who's there?!
[VOICE] The elf only
existed to allow you
to fulfill your purpose.
[ASHRAM]
My purpose?
[VOICE] Do you wish to
become Wagnard's puppet?
Wagnard?
[VOICE] He has no intention
of following you.
[ASHRAM]
Huh. That is no surprise.
[VOICE]
The Scepter of Domination.
What do you think is
Wagnard's real intent?
[VOICE laughs]
I imagine even Kardis
would have to submit to it.
Who the devil are you?
[VOICE] The demon sword,
Soul Crusher.
It would appear
you've mastered it.
But will it serve you
against Kardis?
[ASHRAM]
What are you saying?
[VOICE]
The boy known as Parn.
He will surely come
to Marmo as well.
That kid, Parn.
Why, it's you!
[KARLA]
Return to Marmo.
All Lodoss must now
go there as well.
[PARN] You want me to carry this
message to the people of Moss?
[KASHUE] Shadam will go
to Raiden. We must gather
all the forces of
Lodoss for this task.
The Marmo... They must have
the Scepter of Domination.
The Scepter of Domination?
Legends say that whoever holds
the Scepter of
Domination rules Lodoss.
Oh, come on, Deed.
With Ashram and Beld dead,
no one's left.
[KASHUE] No.
Something else is going on.
Something's changing on Marmo.
You mean like long-scattered
forces uniting again?
Well, count me out. This stuff
sounds like nonsense.
Legends has it that
Kardis the Destroyer
still sleeps beneath
the dark island of Marmo.
[gasps]
Kardis... the Destroyer...
[PARN] Karids? Resurrected
on the island of Marmo?
If it's true, we're too late.
[gasps]
Deedlit...
[WAGNARD laughs]
So this is the Scepter
of Domination.
The power is mine.
Not even Kardis
can overcome
the power of the scepter.
[chuckles]
Now Lodoss will be yours
to control, Lord Wagnard.
[WAGNARD chuckles]
"Omnipotent power,
creator of all things,
forged from chaos by the gods.
Throw off these false garments
and reveal your true form!
Become a barrier to protect me!"
[laughs]
Kardis, don't delay!
Any time now!
After that...!
[laughs intensely]
[gasps, screams]
[SLAYN]
Come.
[LEYLIA sighs]
You should save those feelings
of concern for Lodoss.
Leylia.
[LEYLIA] I really should be
travelling there alone.
But Slayn... I'm glad
you're here with me.
If things were not so grave,
I'd be able to say the many
things I'd like to.
Oh, Slayn...
[crackling]
Oh no...
Ah... It can't be!
Here, we part company.
Don't get your
hopes up about Raiden.
A free city with no leader.
They couldn't care less about
outsiders or other kingdoms.
We aren't outsiders.
After all, Raiden is
part of Lodoss, too.
Listen to me,
if you're not a friend
or a threat,
you're an outsider.
I guess that's how
you mercenaries think.
Yup! That's why we're
bowing out of this job.
Eh, Orson?
[SHADAM] Go where you will, but
as long as you oppose Marmo,
our paths will
surely cross again.
Best of luck. Hyah!
Bye!
Whoa! Hey, hey! Shiris!
Thanks for everything!
[KASHUE]
It's up to you.
My lord.
Our border forces
should be assembled
and ready to leave soon.
[KASHUE]
Good.
Whoa!
[DEEDLIT]
What's wrong?
Deedlit, I wanna know if you're
still upset about Shiris.
Of course not.
Well, then, what's wrong?
Deed.
[DEEDLIT]
The Marmo... will need me.
[PARN]
Huh...?
[DEEDLIT] Not me... so much as
my powers as a High Elf.
[DEEDLIT] The Marmo,
the Scepter of Domination,
and me.
I don't know who
is behind all of this,
but I have... this feeling that
I know what's happening now,
and it really frightens me.
Deedlit...
Oh, Parn...
[thunder cracks]
[BOTH gasp]
[horses whinny]
[chuckles] The search
is over, my High Elf.
[ORSON]
The sky looks strange.
That's where Parn was headed.
[SIRIS gasps]
Hey, you! What's your name?!
Heh! My name? Wagnard!
Though, soon, you shall
call me your god!
What?!
It's Kardis!
It can't be!
[gasps, screams]
[PARN]
Eeyah!
[yells]
Stop it! Parn, a sword
is no match for him!
[WAGNARD]
"Baylos, almighty power
of fiery destruction,
come forth!"
[PARN groans]
"Friend Undine, spirit of
water. Lend us your power."
[WAGNARD]
Heh!
Hah! Elemental spirits
are no match.
[BOTH gasping]
[PARN grunting]
[WAGNARD laughs]
Enough of this farce.
Now, Deedlit! Run for it!
Parn!
[PARN yells]
[gasps]
Parn!
[DEEDLIT gasps]
Deedlit!
[PARN screams]
--Parn!
--[PARN] Deed!
[WAGNARD]
Hmph! What a fool!
[PARN screams]
You can't... have her...!
I won't let you...!
--[gasps]
--[PARN screams]
[continues screaming]
Deed...!
[WAGNARD]
Hmph.
That will teach you.
Help!
[PARN]
Deed...! [grunts]
--[gasps]
--Shiris, take cover!
But Parn's--
"Spirit of light, become a
beacon and show them the way."
[SLAYN gasps]
[PARN groans]
Deed...
Don't worry. You're all right.
[PARN gasps]
Yes, you're safe now, Parn.
[SLAYN] Etoh's treatment alone
wasn't enough to save you.
But Slayn...
[grunts]
Deedlit. Where is she, Slayn?
[PARN grunts]
Parn, you're still too weak!
But if I don't get Deed back,
that wizard will...!
She'll...!
I've gotta find her!
Parn, calm down.
But!
Deedlit probably used
the last of her powers
to gather
the spirits of light.
The light she gave turned your
father's sword into a beacon.
That is what lead us
here to find you.
[SLAYN] The one who took her
was probably Wagnard.
Yes, he's the one.
The eternal life
of a High Elf...
Such infinite power
would be necessary
to resurrect the dark goddess.
Use Deed's life to...
revive Kardis.
Help!
[PARN grunts]
[PARN]
Deed...
[PARN grunts]
Deed...!
[grunts]
Deed!
Deed...!
[SHIRIS] Where are you going
without even a sword?
What's the matter, Parn?
Got a death wish?
And what about that letter
King Kashue gave you?
It has to be delivered to Moss.
Ugh! So stubborn.
We'll take it to Moss, Parn.
[SHIRIS]
Orson!
I think Shiris was thinking of
doing it already. Weren't you?
--[SHIRIS sighs]
--Orson...
Hey, do you think my buddy and I
aren't right for this job?
Of course not.
Listen up. Just don't die
before I see you again.
[horse whinnies]
What're you doing?!
I see you're still as
stubborn as you ever were.
Parn, Princess Fianna
wants you to have this.
--But that's...
--[ETOH] King Fahn's sword.
--Etoh.
--She said that you
should carry it, Parn.
To Marmo then.
[NARRATOR] Beld is no more.
Fahn is no more.
Within this chaos,
who shall be the one
to gain control of Lodoss?
Even now, the full might
of Lodoss moves toward
a final battle with
the forces of darkness
on the island of Marmo.
And does Ashram
still have a chance
to realize his ambitions?
Let all the wonders
come to me
The fantasy fills,
fills my heart
I'll never wander anymore
For all the love I have,
I have for you
All the spirits of the wind
Spread their magic
wings and fly
Racing at the speed of light
Through the valleys
and the passages of time
When we fell in love
Destiny
Now each night
will have no end
Our nights will never end
Eternity awaits
You and me
Now that you are here
We'll never be alone again
Stay with me, my love