[ALDO]
Lady Neese!
Wh-What's going on here?!
--[WAGNARD chuckles]
--[NEESE gasping]
Now, Doorway, you will
accompany me to the dark island.
[NEESE gasping]
No!
[gasps]
[NEESE whimpers]
It is your destiny.
You cannot fight it.
Please, stop! No!
What's wrong?!
I-It must be...
the dark nightmare!
It is the will of the gods.
I am following a dark nightmare.
[screaming]
[SPARK]
Damn it...!
[SPARK grunting]
[GREEVUS]
"Great god of War!
Grant peace to this
person's tortured heart!"
"Manna of creation!
Free this innocent girl
from the dark wizard's grip!"
[ALL groaning]
[WAGNARD chuckles, groans]
Uh! Neese!
[exhales]
[footsteps]
[GUARD A]
What's going on?!
[RYNA]
Spark!
[WAGNARD exhales]
[WAGNARD] So, they combine
their powers to interfere!
Heh... But it doesn't matter.
I already possess the first
key... the Soul Crystal Ball.
And when I acquire the
second key, we will meet again.
[WAGNARD laughs]
Lock the fortress gates!
Split into two groups!
Commence scouting operation!
[knocking]
The intruder may
have been a Dark Elf
looking for revenge.
It is safest for
you to remain here.
Leave the rest to us.
He's got no clue.
There's no way a
Dark Elf could do this.
Well, we just can't sit
around here doing nothing.
Am I right?
[ALDO]
Forget it.
The one who did this
is nowhere near us.
As Leaf said, this is not
the work of Dark Elves.
I don't think the real enemy
will attack again anytime soon.
[ALDO]
So for now, we can do nothing.
Aldo...
The dark nightmare...
[gasps]
That is what I
heard you say before.
Aldo, I think you know what's
going on here. Don't you?
[SPARK]
Then tell us what it is, Aldo!
Why did this happen to Neese?
What is going on here?!
[ALDO sighs] It's just...
It's just that...
Aldo!
A-All right. I'll tell. But you
should prepare yourselves.
After you know the truth,
nothing will ever
be the same again.
[GARRACK]
Heh, what's that supposed mean?
You'll see...
[SPARK]
Wh-What did you say?!
That stolen crystal ball is
the key to reviving Kardis?!
[ALDO]
Yes, it is.
Kardis is the
Goddess of Destruction,
her only purpose is to
destroy the entire world.
If Kardis is revived,
it'll be worse than war!
All of Flaim and all of Marmo
will be destroyed
at the same time!
I had no idea
that the treasure we're
chasing was this important.
There is an ancient legend.
Is says:
Two keys and one door,
and Kardis shall live once more.
But, what does it mean?
[ALDO] When two objects
for the advent of Kardis
are brought together,
and a special sacrifice is made,
the Goddess of Destruction
shall be reborn.
One of the objects is
the Soul Crystal Ball
which has the power
to resurrect the dead.
The other is the Staff of Life,
which is able to heal
all wounds on a body.
But, you also said something
about a special sacrifice.
That special sacrifice
is the person
who has received
the soul of Naneel--
the High Priestess of Kardis
who was killed during
the War of Heroes.
And it is Neese's mother,
the priestess Leylia,
who has received that soul.
[ALL gasp]
There are two keys
and one door...
And the evil had
of the dark wizard
is at the center of it all.
The dark nightmare...
It's Wagnard.
[gasps]
Hey, hold on a minute.
Why is he going after Neese?
If what you just said is true,
shouldn't he be going
after Leylia? Well?
[ALDO] That's what everyone
assumed from the beginning.
However...
It is said that the
sacrifice must be young
and of pure blood.
So when Leylia gave
birth to a child,
she was no longer qualified
to be the sacrifice.
[ALDO] And since Leylia's blood
was ultimately passed down
to her only daughter...
But... But that means--
[NEESE]
Yes. I am the one.
I am "The Doorway"
and now you know.
[ALDO] When she
learned of her destiny,
Lady Neese set out on her own
to prevent Kardis' resurrection.
Prepared to face the
darkest of sorcerers.
This... This young girl...
An innocent.
She's committed
no sin of her own!
It... can't be...
[birds chirping]
Does all of this news suddenly
shock you, Master Spark?
Yes.
Uh! I mean, no! I mean...
It's all right.
I was shocked, too,
when I first learned about this.
But now...
[SPARK]
I... I'm sorry! Because we-- No,
because I did not recover
the Soul Crystal Ball.
[NEESE] Master Spark,
it wasn't your fault.
Please, just call
me Spark, okay?
[laughs]
Okay. Just Spark, then.
Please don't torture
yourself over this.
This is my fate and I accept it.
Even if the crystal ball
had never been stolen,
this still would have happened.
Yes, but how...? You're fighting
against a dark wizard!
How can you possibly
expect to beat him?
You really should find a safe
place to hide instead.
You've already seen it yourself.
There's no safe place for me
to hide from Wagnard's reach.
So why should I try?
[SPARK]
Huh? Oh...
It's all right.
And besides, the battle hasn't
been decided yet, Spark.
My next step is to make
sure that the Staff of Life
is still safe.
The Staff of Life?!
[SPARK] Of course! If they
can't get the other key,
then Neese's bloodline
wouldn't make a difference!
I believe that the Staff of Life
is held in the holy
temple of Valis.
If it's guarded by the holy
royal knights of Valis,
then we're safe.
Valis...
[GARRACK]
What?! We're setting out again?!
You heard me!
Now that we know the
crystal ball isn't here,
I can see no point in us
hanging around anymore!
And we've still got this.
[GREEVUS] Uh? The dispatch
from King Kashue
to King Etoh of Valis.
[SPARK] Now we can deliver
the king's message.
And perhaps I can help to
keep Neese safe as well.
[SPARK] All right,
prepare yourselves at once!
We have a vital duty to
get this message to Valis!
We are leaving right away.
Actually, going to Valis
now is a very good idea.
And if we're lucky, we may
even come across the courier
with the stolen crystal ball.
[BOTH]
Huh?
What are you saying?
Just think about it.
If the crystal ball
has already been handed
off to a courier...
...the fastest way for
someone to get it to Marmo
is to get a ship at the
port of Roodo in Kanon.
And since Kanon is already
under Marmo occupation,
it would also be the safest way.
It's just common sense when
you really think about it.
But aren't Flaim's forces
covering all of the roads
leading to Kanon?
You're right, Leaf.
That means they'll have to
find a back door out of here.
[GARRACK] The only way to
reach Marmo is by sea.
And if you can't use
Roodo to get a ship...
[SPARK] Of course! You'd have to
go to the port of Roid in Valis!
Now you've got it!
So going to Valis is smart.
Hey, you think like a thief.
Watch your mouth.
[GARRACK, RYNA]
Mm?
You're right, Ryna! Now we might
still recover the crystal!
Oh, thank you!
Thank you so much, Ryna!
Please, you really don't
have to thank me... Heh.
[GARRACK]
Sheesh, how naive can you get?
Now all we've
got to think about
is how to handle
that dark wizard.
[ALL]
Mm...
We already know that
he can appear anywhere
he wants to, right?
Now, if he targets us
while we're traveling,
it could be trouble.
[ALDO] We won't have to
worry about him for a while.
[ALL]
Huh?
Long ago, the master
wizard Ralkas
placed a curse on all dark
wizards as punishment
for staining their hands with
the practice of black magic.
[ALDO] Since then, whenever a
dark wizard uses magic,
he must endure excruciating
pain throughout his body.
But then, this guy must...
Indeed. He cast that spell in
spite of the terrible pain
it caused him.
To have that kind of will
means he's no ordinary man.
Yes. But even the most
powerful dark wizard
would need time to recover after
casting a spell like that.
It will be a while
before we see him again.
And even if he does decide to
appear again, fine with me.
I shall protect Neese
with my own two hands!
You're so brave!
[SPARK] I will not allow Wagnard
to lay a finger on Neese!
No matter what!
[LEAF] Especially since
she's one of us now!
Right, everybody?
[GARRACK]
Right.
Thank you all.
Man. I never expected this.
All we were supposed to do was
keep our hotheaded captain safe.
Well, now. Are we scared because
we're facing a dark wizard,
Mr. Blue Meteor?
[growls] Shut your mouth!
You know that's not the point!
I'll see this thing through,
no matter what!
[RYNA]
Hmph.
[GARRACK grunts]
Well, now that we've got a plan,
why don't you give us
your orders, Captain?
[SPARK]
All right, everyone, let's go!
To the holy kingdom of Valis!
[NARRATOR] With fervent hope
and some nagging fears,
Spark and the others set out
for the holy kingdom of Valis.
At the same time, hoping to
free Kanon from Marmo control,
Parn and Deedlit ride
toward the secret base
of Kanon's free army.
Ahh. We finally made it.
Our new base is the hidden
fortress of Kanon's free army.
Eh...? That's it...?
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[MAAR] When I heard there
was an army of partisans
taking on the Marmo,
I expected their fortress to
be a little more impressive.
[sighs]
This place might as well
be a bandit's hideout!
Ah, well. Guess there
won't be any big
welcoming feast for us tonight.
Have you forgotten
that we're at war?
And we're actually
behind enemy lines?
What did you expect?
Really. You wanted
to come along.
Well, you could always
go home by yourself Maar.
[MAAR] Uh, oh. I guess the elf
princess must be mad at me
for getting in the way of her
lovely, romantic trip with Parn.
Maar!
[sighs]
[HOBB]
Huh? Oh...
Parn! Deedlit!
It's been a while, Priest Hobb.
You're well?
Huh? I don't believe it!
It's Priest Hobb!
[HOBB]
Maar? What are you doing here?
Huh? We've got Kanon
trapped by the Marmo,
a free army amasses
to fight them,
and Parn's come to lead!
If you ask me, it's got
"saga" written all over it!
Sure it does.
l thought you were on a quest to
find true heroes, Priest Hobb.
And it's always led me
back to the same place.
Please, come inside.
Everyone's been
awaiting your arrival.
[PARN] Have there been any
new developments, Hobb?
The situation in the
villages remains the same.
But there's disturbing news.
What is it, Priest Hobb?
It seems the Marmo Council
is not too happy
with Governor
Rabido's dictatorship.
It looks like we'll be getting
a new governor any time now.
l doubt that the peoples'
anger will subside
just because the Marmo
council is sending
a new tyrant to rule over them.
Perhaps. But a new ruler will
mean a change in our strategy.
That's why Prince Reona
is waiting to fill you in.
[PARN]
Very good. Let's go.
Who is Prince Reona?
He's the leader
of the free army.
Prince Reona is
the only rightful heir
to throne of Kanon.
I can't believe it.
Another hero fighting
to protect and preserve
the future of Lodoss.
Ah, ha, ha! My poet's
blood is boiling up!
[MAAR laughs]
[RABIDO laughs]
[RABIDO]
My treasures are still fabulous!
No matter how many
times I look at them.
[laughs]
[RABIDO sighs]
[RABIDO] Precious gems are
like tasty bits of food to me!
Oh, I like this governor
business just fine!
[RABIDO laughs]
[RABIDO] Hm?! Hey, Slaves!
Bring me some more wine!
[WOMEN]
Oh...
[yelp]
[chuckles]
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've
been waiting for,
the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
Now, to bring you
all up to date...
We're still wandering
around in this cavern.
We've been walkin' in circles.
Spark's got no freakin'
sense of direction.
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ha, ha!
How come you're
being so mean?! Waa!
If I knew it was
gonna be like this,
I'd have stayed in Flaim
and picked up chicks!
[PARN] This is no time
to be blowing your nose!
Who are you?! Show yourself!
Gee! You're so brave!
[SPARK]
Ahh!
[NEESE, SPARK scream]
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Yee-haw!
[PARN] Running away is
really embarrassing, Spark!
Could that be...?
Yes! It's Parn!
[PARN]
Well, it ain't your momma!
[belches]
I've been running
around this stupid place
for over a month now!
[BOTH yelp]
We're so hungry!
Please give us food!
[PARN] Here's an important
lesson for you, Spark...
A knight must
always be prepared.
[DEEDLIT] Yeah! Always make
sure you have enough food.
Hey! Who's teaching who here?!
But it's okay!
You guys missed me so much
that you came out searching!
Hey! A camera!
Air time!
[SPARK] I've tried to follow
all of your advice, Parn.
Like, no matter what plan
I choose to follow,
I shouldn't get careless.
No matter what, I'm going
to complete this mission
and become a great knight!
So, from now on...
Hey, Parn! Deedlit! Hey!
What are you doing?!
Hi!
They're so starved for air time,
they'll do anything
to get on camera now.
Just cut it out!
This is our TV show now!
[laughs]
[ALL]
We'll be seeing you!
[PARN] The free army rises up to
save Kanon and smash the Marmo!
As we begin the battle,
the Black Knight, who we last
saw at Fire Dragon Mountain,
reappears with a new ambition!
Once again,
we must face the man
who wields the
demon sword, Ashram!
Next time,
on Record of Lodoss War:
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"An Old Enemy...
Reunion with the Black Knight."