[WAGNARD]
You insignificant flea!
How dare you corrupt
the Doorway's heart?!
The sacrifice to Kardis
must remain pure!
I'll not let you interfere.
It's Wagnard!
[SPARK gasps]
The time has come
for me to take you.
And now, we shall journey
to the dark island.
It is your destiny.
You cannot fight it.
[NEESE]
No! Let me go!
[SPARK growls]
"Darkness of the blackest pitch,
I command you to
become a dark shield
and repel this aggressor!"
[gasps] Spark!
Spark, run!
[SPARK growls]
[yells]
[chuckles]
Heh.
[SPARK grunts]
No, Spark!
And now, Doorway,
we shall return to the
dark island of Marmo.
[NEESE]
Spark! Spark! Spark...!
Neese!
Lady Neese...
Lady Neese... [sobs]
[ALDO sobbing]
This is nothing but a
giant waste of time.
Garrack!
Come on, Leaf. We're fighting
against a dark wizard.
He's got Neese exactly
where he wants her,
on the dark island of Marmo.
Dammit! We should team up with
the free army and go after her.
I don't see the point.
Now Wagnard's finally got
the sacrifice he needs
to revive Kardis...
And that means...
[GARRACK groans]
[RYNA]
Spark...
I failed once again.
[RYNA]
Huh?
[SPARK] I couldn't protect
the Soul Crystal Ball
or the Staff of Life.
And now, I've lost Neese.
Oh, Neese.
[SPARK growls]
No!
[RYNA]
Spark!
Now wait a minute, Spark.
What do you think you're doing?
What does it look like I'm
doing?! I'm going after Neese!
[RYNA] What do you mean
you're going after her?
Now think, Spark.
[PARN] If you just go
to Marmo without a plan,
you will die needlessly.
[gasps]
You cannot undo
what's been done.
Now just calm down
and think this over.
But... I have thought
this through!
Neese has been kidnapped
and it's my fault!
Are you saying there's
something else I can do?!
Stop it, Spark!
[gasps]
[PARN]
I understand how you feel,
but you can't think clearly
when you're this angry.
Now listen: We're going ahead
with my plans as I've made them.
We will join up with Prince
Ryona and retake Roodo.
If we're successful, then
we can cross into Marmo
without so much as a scratch.
But how long?
How long will it be before
we can cross over into Marmo?
I don't know.
But, for right now,
this is our only
sure path toward
finally striking back at Marmo.
You cannot undo
what's been done.
[gasps]
Tomorrow morning,
we leave for Roodo.
[SPARK whimpers]
[SPARK] Oh, why can't I
just abandon everything
and go after her?!
For all we know, right now,
Neese could be...!
Please calm down.
[SPARK]
I've got to decide right now...
I've got to determine the
best way to save Neese.
[NEESE grunts, gasps]
Where am I?
[growling]
[gasps]
[NEESE sighs]
[NEESE]
Oh, Spark...
I know you'll come...
[NEESE] "O great Marfa,
mother of the Earth...
Grant me your divine protection.
Please return me to my home."
The power of the dark
goddess is interfering.
[WAGNARD chuckles]
[NEESE gasps]
[WAGNARD] So, Doorway,
you're finally awake.
I welcome you to the
dark island of Marmo.
It's Wagnard!
What's wrong? Won't your
goddess answer your prayers?
[WAGNARD laughs]
Then again, you are in a
shrine dedicated to Kardis,
the almighty Goddess
of Destruction.
Your powers are useless here,
and the knight who defends you
is far, far away.
But Wagnard, why would
you even attempt
to resurrect someone as evil
as the Goddess of Destruction?
[WAGNARD]
Why would I? Hmph!
Is it not natural for one
who is great and powerful
to seek even greater power?
[gasps]
It was for that reason
alone that I was able
to acquire the forbidden spells.
Those fools at the Academy of
Sages cast me out of their
mystic brotherhood when they
discovered what I had done,
forcing me to endure the torment
of the spells I'd stolen.
But alas, I shall not
have suffered in vain.
You're a sick man.
What do you want from this?
[WAGNARD]
Ah...
When Kardis is reborn, all will
be consumed by darkness.
The people, the land,
every living creature
will be destroyed.
But for me, the annihilation
of the world will be
the beginning of a new era.
At last, I will exact my revenge
against those who mocked me.
I alone shall reign supreme as
Lord of the Kingdom of the Dead.
That's why...? That's why?
I can't believe you're about
to destroy all of Lodoss
over some petty revenge plot!
Now I'll never let you get
away with this! I swear it!
And you believe that
you can stop me?
Do not forget that within your
body is the soul of Naneel,
High Priestess of
Kardis the Destroyer.
And the one who
controls her is me!
[gasps]
I shall keep you here for
the time being so that
your mind and body
will remain pure.
The time of your sacrifice
is almost at hand.
[WAGNARD laughs]
[NEESE] I can't just sit here...
but there's no escape.
For now, I must have faith
in Marfa's divine protection,
and... and Spark...
Get ready, everyone.
Once we're over this hill,
we'll be very close.
Woo-hoo! Soon I'll be able
to finish my ballad
of the retaking of Kanon.
"And the free knight's
sword took down
the mighty black knight,"
I hope.
Why would you hope for that?
Hey, whose side are
you on, anyway?
Parn, look.
[PARN]
Hmm?
[SPARK]
This is the right thing to do.
It's the smartest and safest
way to get closer to Neese.
Even if it is just a small step,
at least it's a step in
the right direction.
[MAAR]
Whoa! Hey, everyone, look!
[SPARK gasps]
[SPARK]
Th-That must be...
[PARN]
Yes. The dark island of Marmo.
[ALL gasping]
[SPARK] She's there...
Neese is on that island.
[NARRATOR] As Parn and his group
unite with Prince Reona's forces
near Roodo, King Kashue
leads the victorious army
of Flaim from Alania
toward Roodo as well.
It is hoped that
the amassing force
will be sufficient to drive
the remaining Marmo
from the interior of Lodoss.
[NARRATOR] Back in the holy
capital of the kingdom of Valis,
having swept the Marmo forces
from his land in a holy war,
King Etoh loudly proclaims his
decision to engage the Marmo
in one final battle.
We have regained the
protection of Falis here
in our holy kingdom.
But the power of the dark god
still looms as a threat
to all of Lodoss.
So long as the God of Light
shines his protection over us,
let us join our allies
and smash the dark island!
Let us win a true and lasting
peace for all of Lodoss!
[cheering]
[KARLA] Where did I let
things go so wrong?
When I set the balance
of power in Lodoss,
it seemed so easy to control
the ambitions of kings.
Not anymore.
[REONA] We now know that
the Marmo forces hold Roodo
at four key positions.
[REONA] Once we break
through their perimeter,
we will have to hit their four
strongholds simultaneously.
This will eliminate
any chance for Ashram
to concentrate his
troops at the mansion.
[PARN] You're saying we
should hit them hard
while their forces
are still divided.
And if we hit them
all at the same time,
then Ashram and the Marmo
forces won't stand a chance.
That's exactly right.
Which leaves only
the question of
who will take the city center.
Your name's Spark, right?
Uh, yes, sir!
[REONA] I was thinking of
letting your group handle that.
How 'bout it?
Huh?
What?
Your unit has a sorcerer,
a priest of Myrii,
and a grass runner,
which makes it the
strongest unit by far.
They also have a shamanist.
[SPARK]
Taking the city center?
They're giving such an important
duty to me? I don't believe it!
Taking the city center
shall require small numbers
and great mobility.
This is the right move.
I know you can do this, Spark.
Uh! Yes, sir!
[LEAF]
Hmm...
Huh?
It's a big role...
It sounds like fun.
Yes, of course!
You can count on us.
[REONA] Mm-hmm. We will
move into our positions
under the cover of darkness
and attack at first light.
And may the gods
protect you all.
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
[SOLDIERS chattering]
Boy, you dwarves really
are handy with the knife.
What is that thing?
Oh, this? It's just
a little toy.
A toy?
He's joking with you, Leaf.
That's going to become one
powerful little weapon.
[GREEVUS]
Don't listen to him, Leaf.
This really is nothing special.
[SPARK] Tomorrow... Tomorrow...
If this operation works,
the way to Marmo will be clear.
And once it is...
[RYNA] What're you
thinking about, Spark?
[SPARK] Ryna. Never mind,
it wasn't important.
[ALDO]
I know how you feel, Spark.
Try to relax.
Keep your head clear.
We have a most important
job to do tomorrow
and we cannot afford to fail.
[SPARK] Don't worry about me,
Aldo. I know what I must do.
I will not allow myself
to fail again.
Parn and the prince have
put their trust in me
and I must get to the dark
island to save Neese.
Please... All of you,
listen to me!
I need your support
now more than ever.
Don't let me down.
[GREEVUS grunts]
[GARRACK grunts]
[wolf howling]
What? Karla?
Yes. If the reports we received
from other parts of Lodoss
are correct, it must be her.
The Gray Witch is here?
In Kanon? Why?
And at a time when a major
battle is about to begin...
I doubt that Karla would
ever ally herself
with the forces of
Valis or Flaim.
But, if she's making a
move here in Kanon....
Groder, what does
the Marmo council say?
Sir. What they always say.
We received a message telling us
to defend Roodo to the last man.
That was all that it said.
[ASHRAM]
Hmm. It's exactly the response
that I'd expect from them.
Very well. Pirotess!
[PIROTESS]
Sir!
I want you to
prepare some ships.
As many ships as you can find.
It seems the enemy's
allied against me
are not my only concern.
There's definitely something
else at work here.
Sir.
[ASHRAM] Dammit, Wagnard.
What are you up to?
[KARLA] The ancient kingdom
of Kastuul was destroyed
because the sorcerers
who lived there
forgot their limits
as human beings.
And, at this rate, if
the seeds taking root here
in Roodo break through, then...
[GARRACK grunts]
[GREEVUS growls]
Captain! I think it's
time we got going.
[SPARK]
It's almost time.
No matter what happens,
I swear I will save you.
So please, wait for me, Neese.
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've
all been waiting for,
the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
[SPARK]
Somebody actually expects us
to use this to cross?!
[NEESE] One little slip
and we're freakin' dead.
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Freakin' a!
[BOTH gulp]
Oh, wha--!
You go first.
All right.
[creaking]
[NEESE, SPARK whimper]
[screams]
Hey, Neese!
[NEESE]
Pervert!
[DARK ELF]
I see youse two
haven't changed
a bit there, huh?
You oughta know the drill
by now there, cookie-head.
All you gotta do is hand
over them there cookies
and you can all be safe.
Otherwise, I cut
these here ropes.
[NEESE]
That ain't freakin' fair!
[LITTLE DRAGON growls]
[SPARK] No, Little Dragon!
If you toast him again,
you'll burn down the bridge!
Shut up, you!
Now what's it gonna be?
Cookies or death?
I hate to say it, but I think
we should give him the cookies.
Your safety is more
important, Neese.
[PARN]
Hold it, Spark!
Look, it's Parn!
[panting] I'm not an old man!
[PARN snores]
Well, well, if it ain't
that there sissy boy Parn.
[SPARK] Parn, you're the best!
You came to save us!
Uh, no. I just remembered
why I came.
Here, Spark. This is
for yo-- [screams]
[screaming]
[DARK ELF]
Whoopty-doo!
[NEESE, SPARK, DARK ELF]
We'll be seeing you!
[SPARK] The free army
begins to close in.
Their goal? To free Kanon
from the Marmo.
It's the free knight
versus the black knight
in a battle that will
determine the future.
And it's my only chance
to open a path
to the dark island of
Marmo and save Neese.
I cannot afford to lose!
Not this fight!
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War :
Chronicles of
the Heroic Knight :
"Liberation...
A Path Opened."