[NARRATOR]
Light and darkness...
The final battle of the gods
climaxed in a clash between
Marfa, goddess of all creation,
and Kardis, goddess
of destruction.
At the end of their
fierce battle,
the stricken goddesses
had split the continent,
forming a new land.
Since then, people have come
to call this new continent
"Lodoss - The Accursed Island."
The way that you
embrace me with your
strong and powerful arms
Your haunting words keep me
close to everything about you
Romantic in ways
in ways that almost
tear upon my heart
Can't let you go
Don't you know?
Io sono prigioniera
A captive in
your gentle hands
A prisoner of
your soulful eyes,
your special smile
will never part
If the morning sun
should free me
It really wouldn't let me go
I'd still be caught
inside your love
Can't rise above
the chains of your heart
[yelling, groaning]
[SOLDIER A screams]
[MAN A]
Let's get out of here!
[MAN B] Get the women and
children under cover!
Quickly! Move it!
Go now, Ashram.
[BELD] Smashing this place will
have to draw Fahn out to me.
[SOLDIER B yells]
I curse you!
[yells]
[BELD] Soon now, you will
meet your true enemy.
[FAHN]
He comes.
[NARRATOR] Having learned the
intentions of the witch, Karla,
Parn and his companions
leave Wort's castle
and race back to Valis.
However, the advance of Marmo
and their dark emperor, Beld,
is far greater than anyone
in Valis had anticipated.
Where the forces
of darkness pass,
only scorched earth is left
behind for the survivors.
And despair that no amount
of prayer could ever heal.
[PARN gasps]
[MAN C groaning]
[PARN grunts]
Can you hear me?
Hey, are you all right?
Hang on!
[groans]
[DEEDLIT sniffles]
[WOODCHUCK sighs]
[PARN]
How could they do this?
This is what happens
to people in a war.
No knight of Valis could ever
be as cruel as this!
--[WOODCHUCK] Uh-huh...
--[DEEDLIT] Perhaps...
But war shows no
prejudice to its victims.
Soldiers, villagers, women,
children, the elderly...
No one escapes death in battle.
[SLAYN] Parn!
We've been thinking that
you should go back
to King Fahn ahead of us.
[PARN] Slayn! I can't abandon
people who need my help!
Just let us handle
things here, Parn.
King Fahn must be told
about what's happened
here today, Parn.
Yes, but--
[MEN groaning, coughing]
You're right.
Well, we'd better get
going then. Right, Parn?
Uh-huh...
My, how lovey-dovey.
Etoh...
We will all do
the best that we can.
--[PARN] Hyah!
--[DEEDLIT] Hyah!
Hey, come on,
you two! Wait for me!
I'm coming with you!
[fire crackling]
[laughing]
[gasps]
[ASHRAM]
King Kashue's advance party
will be departing
Valis tomorrow.
If our information is correct,
we'll probably meet
somewhere around here.
Hmm... Ashram, take your forces
and join with the elves.
Then, set out ahead of us.
You mean a
sneak attack, my lord?
If we don't change
our battle plan,
we'll surely meet
our end in no time.
Our losses are not sacrifices.
They're a necessary shield.
As you will be if you die.
Yes, sire. As you may be, too.
[BELD chuckles]
[laughing]
[MARMO A]
Why you...!
[DARK ELF A] Pirotess is
one of the greatest
of the Dark Elf women.
She'll have nothing
to do with human men.
Oh yeah?! Are you
tellin' me that elves
are better than humans?
Are you saying
that we're not?
Why you...! Aah!
--[yells]
--[laughter]
[MARMO A]
I'll get you!
[yells]
--Now die!
--[whimpers]
Hey, captain!
Well, that'll teach you
to mess around with us!
[MARMO A yelps]
Know this! Men who
don't know their limits
have no place here!
Yes... Yes, sir...
[FAHN]
You've returned safely.
[PARN]
Yes, Your Majesty.
[FAHN]
Tell me what you've learned.
The Great Sage,
Wort, told me that
Karla is a survivor
of the Kingdom of Sorcery.
[WORT] For these past 500 years,
in different forms and guises,
when the balance of Lodoss
is tipped, she appears.
She uses her power to affect
the course of history.
Prince and peasant alike
are merely pawns to her,
or so she believes.
So now, we're all
pawns in a game.
[footsteps]
[KASHUE]
Is that Parn I hear?
King Kashue! My lord!
Is it really you? Don't go
and fade away on me now!
[laughs]
Hey!
King Kashue, if you keep
knocking him around like that,
he'll break before too long!
[PARN]
Uh, uh, Deed...
Aw... [laughs]
Forgive me, please.
Parn, there is something I
would like to present to you.
[gasps]
That's-- That's--
[FAHN] The armor of a
Holy Knight. My gift to you.
Would you wear it and
fight bravely by my side?
[FAHN]
Parn?
Your Highness, I would
like to ask a favor of you.
[FAHN]
Mm?
[PARN] I appreciate
your thoughtful gift
with all my heart.
It's just that...
the sword and the armor left
to me by my father, Tessius,
are the only ones
I'll ever need to carry.
I see.
Well then, why don't
you take this shield?
Since you don't
have one of your own.
Yes!
King Fahn,
the Holy Knights of Valis
have gained a fine
new member on this day!
You'll do well.
Yes, sir!
Tch, come on! Gimme a break!
[KASHUE]
Parn... I'll be waiting.
[PARN]
Sire...
Huh?
[PARN grunts]
Who's there?!
Woodchuck!
If that was meant as a joke,
it wasn't very funny!
Take it easy, Deedlit.
I just wanted to see
what the kid was made of,
you know, with him facing
his first war and all that.
Well, you can just
stop worrying
because I plan to protect
King Fahn no matter what!
No matter how many men
you might have to kill?
--Huh?
--[PARN gasps]
Wood! You talk too much!
Hey, hey! Pretty ladies
shouldn't make scary faces.
It isn't very nice.
Just once, would you
please talk straight?
Well, now that
you're a knight of Valis,
you're probably gonna
wind up forgetting
about all the pain
we saw coming here.
Wood, this has to be done!
If you can't forget it,
you're in trouble.
Because if you don't,
you'll never be able to
kill a man in battle. Eh?
Some choice, huh?
[DEEDLIT]
Parn...
[SOLDIER groaning]
[groaning]
Slayn.
[SLAYN]
Ghim!
You're going after Karla alone,
and you expect to defeat
her without any help?
I don't think I'll win.
So you're throwing
your life away?
[GHIM grunts]
Will rushing into this battle
return Leylia to her mother?
I just can't wait anymore!
[KARLA] "Leylia"? Yes, I believe
that was this body's name.
But all that remains now
is myself. [chuckles]
[GHIM growls]
Once we've finished
with our tasks here,
I promise to go
with you. But for now...
But Slayn, I--
[groans]
[ETOH]
Slayn!
[gasps]
You put a spell on him?
[SLAYN]
The battle is still to come,
but a warrior
like Ghim needs his rest.
Although, I doubt he'd agree.
Uh... Just how soon
will the battle come?
[SLAYN]
Very soon now.
Ghim will fight his,
and Parn will fight his.
Both have battles to wage.
Etoh, whatever happens today,
don't give up hope.
It's best you never forget that.
[ETOH]
Hm.
[PARN] Your Majesty,
you called for me?
Yes. The main force
leaves tomorrow, Parn.
Sire, you'll let
me come, won't you?
Yes, but I don't think
I'll be returning.
Your Highness, please don't
think like that.
What I am about to tell you
would have been
revealed eventually.
Huh?
[FAHN] Do you have time
to listen to an old story?
An old story?
Of when Valis wasn't nearly as
stable a nation as it is today.
I, along with the Holy Knights,
were attempting to form
a union of the various
regions of our land.
And the plan would unite
all of Lodoss. I see.
I didn't want to
do it by force,
so I, along with my knights,
negotiated many treaties.
[TRIBE MAN A] So, the King of
Valis dares to break our treaty!
[FAHN] At that time, one tribe
was being harassed by
Shooting Star, the demon dragon
of Fire Dragon Mountain.
[screaming]
[FAHN] Citing our defense
treaty, the tribe leaders
demanded my newborn daughter,
Fianna, as a sacrifice
to quell the
demon dragon's evil fire.
[FAHN]
But, I... I...!
Taking Fianna back would
have broken the treaty.
But then...
You?
[TESSIUS] I will retrieve
the princess, Your Majesty.
[FAHN]
But--
[TESSIUS] No treaty
is worth a human life.
[FAHN]
Tessius...
[TESSIUS]
This is my plan alone.
It will appear
as if you just have
a bad subordinate
in your ranks.
Isn't that acceptable?
[FAHN]
Fianna was returned safely.
When war finally broke out
with that tribe,
Tessius silently, dutifully
left for the front.
I never saw him again.
I have never so despised my
position as king as I did then.
[PARN]
Father...
[giggles]
I found you!
[music plays]
--[PARN] Deedlit.
--[DEEDLIT] Hm?
--Stay behind tomorrow.
--[music stops]
Deedlit...
I'm coming along.
Look, we don't even know
if we'll be coming back!
Okay, then explain to me
why you have to go!
[sighs]
Because the only thing
I can do now is keep moving on.
That's why I have to go.
Well then, I've got
to go with you.
Because somebody's
got to protect your rear.
Deedlit!
The world is full of people
who will get you from behind.
Let me handle them.
You keep your eyes
on what's ahead.
--[PARN] Deed...
--[music plays]
[music continues]
[DARK ELF A]
By your leave...
Let's go!
Hm?!
Please allow me to
accompany you, my lord.
I promise that
I shall serve you well.
[WAGNARD chuckles]
Tomorrow shall see a mountain
of corpses; a sea of blood!
Kardis, it shall be the greatest
of all sacrifices to you!
[BELD]
Narse... What troubles you?
It is still too soon
for you to emerge.
Your strength is not yet
needed. Wait until it is.
But who? Who is summoning him?
Can it be?
King Kashue, I fear there
is something wrong.
None of our scouts has
come back to report yet.
[KASHUE]
Hm...
My lord, look! It's one
of the scouting party!
[yells]
Trying to confuse us by using
our own men against us!
[yelling, groaning]
Stand firm, men! They're
no better than animals!
They don't know
how to fight! Stand firm!
[yelling, groaning]
[NARRATOR] Thirty years
have come and gone.
And two men once
worshipped as heroes,
now cross swords
for control of Lodoss.
Two friends, who once
fought side by side,
now fight to the death
as their echoes
resound throughout the land.
Their battle
shall become a legend
that will be told
for generations to come.
[cheering]
Let all the wonders
come to me
The fantasy fills,
fills my heart
I'll never wander anymore
For all the love I have,
I have for you
All the spirits of the wind
Spread their magic
wings and fly
Racing at the speed of light
Through the valleys
and the passages of time
When we fell in love
Destiny
Now each night
will have no end
Our nights will never end
Eternity awaits
You and me
Now that you are here
We'll never be alone again
Stay with me, my love