[roars]
[PARN]
Can it be... Another dragon?!
[DEEDLIT]
He's called Narse!
The ancient dragon who
sleeps beneath Marmo!
[ALL gasping]
[KARLA]
Now then, heroes of Lodoss...
...all you have to do
is kill this dragon
if you wish to stop
the Destroyer's return.
[NARSE roars]
[LEAF]
It's huge!
[DEEDLIT] This is a trap!
We were lured here on purpose!
[gasps] What's going on?!
That is Narse. He is one
of the Ancient Dragons,
but the native people
of Marmo have learned
how to domesticate him.
But how? That means that they
can control his actions. [gasps]
It's an enemy I'd really
rather not fight...
...but we don't have
any other choices now.
Spread out now!
[ALL grunting]
Now, Slayn! Cast a
protection spell!
"Manna of all creation,
become a shield to protect us!"
[SPARK]
All right, let's go!
[PARN yells]
[roars]
[gasps]
"Mighty Sylph,
spirit of the wind...
Assume thy form and
repel this attack!"
Garrack! No!
Hyah!
[roars]
[SPARK yells, grunts]
Captain!
"Manna of creation! Become
the fires of destruction!"
[LEAF]
Come on!
[SPARK groans]
[PARN]
Damn, he's tough!
This is getting us nowhere.
He's bound to outlast us, Parn,
so what should we do?
You're right, Deed, but--
[MAAR]
Help us! Help!
Help!
[SLAYN]
"Great Manna of all creation,
become a sword of light
and strike down our enemy!"
Here! Come this way!
Maar!
[SPARK growls]
[MAAR panting]
[screams]
Maar!
[roars]
[gasps]
What's going on here?!
[SHIRIS]
Parn!
[PARN]
Shiris!
Shouldn't the great free
knight be doing something
better than this?
What, are you nuts? We're
fighting an Ancient Dragon here!
What are you doing here?
Last I heard, you and
the Duke were trying
to unify the kingdom of Moss.
I couldn't just sit home during
Lodoss' most important battle!
Parn, I came to bring
you an advance guard!
An advance guard? Huh?
[KARLA growls]
Who are they?
They're the dragon riders
of Highland, Spark!
Now just let us handle him.
Parn, you get to the castle.
Yeah, but--
You'll be in the way! And
besides, I don't want you
underestimating
my dragon riders!
All right, let's go!
Sir Parn!
Captain, we can't stay here.
You're right. Let's go!
We're the ones you're
fighting, pal.
Prepare to attack! But not head
on, or you'll be eating flames!
Let's go!
Damn your meddling.
[PEOPLE screaming]
Are you sure it's the
dragon riders of Highland?
No doubt about it. Right now,
they're battling Narse
out in the forest.
That's impressive. The Moss
border is at least 10 days away,
so they must've come
as a vanguard.
What is the status
of the main force?
They're assembling
offshore to our east.
So, it looks like one
massive attack now.
[ASHRAM]
No doubt.
From Emperor Beld's
glorious dream,
to a strong and powerful
Marmo council, now to this.
I estimate that we've got about
one more day to stay here.
What's the status of
our evacuation plans?
If all goes well, we'll be
ready to go in half a day.
Very well. Good job.
[PIROTESS]
Where are you going, my lord?
[ASHRAM] I cannot leave
here without a word.
I have to see him one last time.
You go on ahead of me.
No, I'll wait here for my man.
I'll be back.
[panting]
There it is! It's Conquera!
[ALL grunting]
[gasps]
[PARN]
That circlet!
[KARLA]
It's been a long time, Leylia.
[gasps]
[KARLA]
And you, heroes of Lodoss.
[SPARK]
Who is she?
[SLAYN] She was one of the Six
Heroes who fought along side
Neese and the others
to save Lodoss.
And now she's the Grey
Witch who brings only
chaos to Lodoss. It's Karla!
Why don't we just fight her?
Wait. I did not come
here to fight you.
I have come with a
final deal for you all.
What sort of deal?
What's on your mind?
We'll hear you out.
[NARSE growls]
[DRAGON RIDERS yelling]
[NARSE roars]
Don't let up on the attack, men!
Keep circling around his head!
Incoming! Look out now!
[DRAGON RIDER screams]
What the--?!
[DRAGON RIDERS screaming]
Pull up!
You sure are a tough one, Narse!
[SHIRIS gasps]
[SHIRIS]
Are we out of time...?
No! We've got to keep
on fighting! Yaah!
[SHIRIS screams]
[KARLA] The history of Lodoss
is a history of war.
Since the beginning of time,
people have fought wars here
again and again.
But why do wars happen?
Have any of you ever thought
about the reason for them?
[SPARK]
The reason for the wars?
[KARLA]
It is power.
People attack other kingdoms,
expand their dominion,
and gain power as a result.
And then they dream of
gaining even more power,
only for themselves.
And they continue, not knowing
where their path will lead.
It doesn't have to
end in destruction.
[LEYLIA]
He's right.
It's true that the great
sorcerers of the ancient kingdom
of Kastuul were destroyed
by their own lust for power.
That's because they forgot
about their limits as people.
But that was only
one possible result.
[SLAYN] Yet, for you,
it was the only result.
And so you've hidden yourself
throughout history,
emerging only to influence
us with the chaos of war
and the eternal fight of
meaningless battles.
[SPARK gasps]
What are you saying?
Karla causes strong kingdoms
to fight against each other.
She believes that keeping all
nations preoccupied with war
will guarantee that none
become too powerful.
What the...?
No kingdom gets more powerful.
In fact, many just
get destroyed.
All I have done has been
for the sake of Lodoss.
There is no good or evil.
No light or darkness.
There is only grey. And that
is where the balance exists.
And now you have become
far too powerful.
And that is a problem.
[ALL gasping]
I see! So that's what
this is all about!
You think we have upset
the balance of power,
and so, you've been trying
to eliminate us
from the moment we
landed here on Marmo.
But why, Karla? Don't you know
that Wagnard is trying
to revive Kardis?
If you kill us and
he is successful,
then all of Lodoss
will be destroyed.
So why are you doing this?
You are correct in your
assumption, High Elf.
That will be the final stage.
[gasps]
[WAGNARD]
"Ladeera ve Kardis.
Vanna dol gel ru deldu vir...
Ladeera vanna dol.
Ladeera rui deer.
Leyri del ra Kardis.
Ledura damu ladora Kardis.
Ladira Ladora Kardis..."
[WAGNARD] "Marta suda vaygloss.
Ladeera ladora Kardis!"
[NEESE whimpers]
[WAGNARD]
"Ladeera ladora Kardis."
[NEESE wails]
[NEESE shrieks]
[WAGNARD pants]
[yells]
[WAGNARD]
Soon now...
Soon I will be freed from
these annoying restrictions.
Soon...
[ASHRAM] So that's the
restriction of Ralkas.
[WAGNARD]
Hmm?
[ASHRAM]
Isn't it, Wagnard?
[WAGNARD]
Who's there?!
Ashram?
Torturing this young girl
as a sacrifice...
It's bad form.
She is a special
sacrifice, Ashram.
She is the Doorway, the conduit
I need to reach out to the gods.
Don't insult me.
Huh?
[ASHRAM] I know about
your plans for Kadis.
[WAGNARD growls]
[ASHRAM]
It doesn't matter, though.
[WAGNARD]
Hmm?!
[ASHRAM] I have no interests
in Kardis the Destroyer,
or in this kingdom of the
dead you wish to create.
You need not fear any
counteraction on my part.
[WAGNARD] Then why have
you come here, Ashram?
I have come to say farewell.
Farewell?
[ASHRAM] I am leaving Marmo. If
the Destroyer is resurrected,
or if the united armies of
Lodoss succeed in defeating you,
one thing is certain:
Tomorrow, the kingdom we know
as Marmo will cease to exist.
I do not wish to run,
but as a general of Marmo,
I must protect my people.
Oh, your people.
[ASHRAM]
Even if a kingdom is destroyed,
as long as its people live,
a true leader will
inherit their desires.
I shall lead the people
of Marmo to a new land,
and there, I shall build
an entirely new kingdom.
Heh! What kind of a kingdom?
[ASHRAM] The kind of kingdom
Emperor Beld would've wanted.
I didn't think you'd understand.
[WAGNARD]
What a fool.
A kingdom of the living
will always perish.
But a kingdom of the dead
can never be destroyed.
A kingdom of the dead is one
that I can possess forever!
And soon, I shall be anointed as
ruler of that eternal kingdom!
[laughs]
[NARSE growls]
[SHIRIS] We've thrown
everything we've got at him,
and he still won't go down.
This one's a monster!
Damn!
[SHIRIS gasps]
[SHIRIS] It's Mycen, the king
dragon! He saved the day!
[BOTH growling]
We did it! We did it!
[SHIRIS] How very sad.
The end of a beautiful dragon
who abandoned his
pride for evil.
[SHIRIS] Thank you, Mycen!
You've saved our lives!
[MYCEN roars]
[KARLA groans]
[PARN]
That roar!
Was Shiris able to kill Narse?
[KARLA] Narse was your final
test, heroes of Lodoss.
Now I see that the
power you possess
will only lead to
great destruction.
Now choose.
Will you quietly submit
your lives to me?
If you don't, the Destroyer
will be released,
and this world will end.
What did you say?!
[gasping]
This is my final offer.
If you sacrifice your lives,
I shall stop the
Destroyer's resurrection.
But if you refuse, I shall
personally help Wagnard,
and the Destroyer
will be released.
Karla...
I think you've become
too powerful.
You heroes of Lodoss
now have the ability
to destroy yourselves and
the dark goddess herself.
You mean, you'd resurrect Kardis
just so we can fight her?!
And for that, you let Neese--
Over my dead body!
Ahh!
Uh... Huh?!
What?!
Is that your answer,
young knight of Flaim?
[growls]
Spark! Forget it!
That's only Karla's shadow!
[SPARK] No way! I fought too
hard for people that I love!
For people I respect,
and for people I've
sworn to protect!
We won't submit to you!
No one is going to sacrifice
himself for you, Karla!
No one! We'll beat Wagnard
by ourselves, you witch!
[SPARK growls]
We won't be your pawns!
Now go! Begone!
[SPARK growls]
[gasps]
[gasps] Sir Parn... I... I...
Yes. Let's go.
We'll save Lodoss together.
And with our own hands.
There it is... Conquera!
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've all
been waiting for,
the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
[SPARK panting]
[NEESE coughs]
Are you okay, Neese?
[LITTLE DRAGON coos]
I don't want you to be freakin'
worried about me...
It's all right, just make
sure you get some rest
so you can get better.
Thanks...
If there's anything I can get
you, anything, just name it
and it's yours.
I want... some...
I want Lodso fruit...
Lodso fruit?
What are they?
Lodso fruit...
Lodso are juicy fruits
native only to Lodoss
which can soothe even
the worst sore throat!
All right, Neese! I'll go out
and find you some Lodso fruit!
You just stay here
and rest, okay?
[LITTLE DRAGON squawks]
Spark wandered all over Lodoss
looking for Lodso fruit,
all for his beloved Neese.
He looked here...
He looked there...
He looked everywhere.
Oh! Here, look!
[DEEDLIT]
Finally, Spark reached the place
where the Lodso fruit grows.
[SPARK panting]
[NEESE whines]
Lodso fruit!
[screams]
[panting]
Lodso fruit...
[gasps] Holy cow! Lodso fruit!
Hey, Neese! I found some! Look!
[NEESE] Hey, what freakin'
kept you, Spark?
Where'd you go? I was tryin'
to freakin' tell you
they were right outside.
[SPARK screams]
Hey, what's wrong?
[NEESE, SPARK]
We'll be seeing you!
[SPARK] The Destroyer's
resurrection is at hand.
Where are you, Neese?!
As we enter the
castle of Conquera,
the black knight Ashram
appears before us once again.
Parn and Ashram conclude their
twisted destinies as always,
with swords drawn.
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War :
Chronicles of the
Heroic Knight .