Now, kill me. Go ahead.
[SHIRIS sobbing]
Orson... Orson...
[SHIRIS]
Orson!
[SHIRIS] You idiot!
You were finally cured,
and then, for my sake...
For my sake, you died.
You fell in love
with me and you died!
[SHIRIS]
But you died for nothing...
You died for nothing.
You died for nothing!
No, Deed.
[ASHRAM]
Ah...
[HOBB]
Can it be?
This is it, Sir Ashram.
There's no doubt.
The Governor's Treasure
is mine at last.
The Scepter of Domination!
And with it...
And with it, I shall turn
Lodoss into my own kingdom!
I alone shall fulfill Emperor
Beld's dream of a united Lodoss!
The day I have
longed for is at hand.
[HOBB]
As you deserve.
[ASHRAM groans]
[roars]
Impossible! How could
he have returned?!
I thought the dragon
had gone off to feed.
Sir Ashram, you can't!
Let's wait for Groder
and the others to join us!
Yes.
[roars]
[KASHUE] According to the
magical spell put upon him
by the governor of Kastuul,
as long as there are men
who desire the
Scepter of Domination,
Shooting Star cannot stray
too far from his nest.
It's King Kashue!
It has been a while,
Priest Hobb.
But it's been far longer,
Sir Ashram, since we last met.
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
It's been a while,
but I still have not been
able to forget your face,
Kashue of Flaim.
[KASHUE]
Shall we end things here?
We both know that if
we are to survive,
the dragon must die.
I want to know if
you will help me.
[ASHRAM]
Are you insulting me?
There is no way that you
and I will ever become allies,
so calm down.
The truth is that I
happen to hate Shoot Star
far more than I hate you.
Dragons and people
aren't the same.
Shooting Star is
an inconvenience,
but I do not hate him.
I do, however, hate you.
[KASHUE]
Let us work together first.
There will be time
enough for our duel
after the demon dragon is dead.
You mean...
[KASHUE] I've heard that
the Scepter of Domination
has the power to make
even your enemies obey you.
First, we'll kill the dragon.
Then, you and I and
our men will fight,
and the ultimate victor
will be the one
to control the
Scepter of Domination!
An interesting offer.
But I've already seen your
dirty tricks in a fight.
Or have you forgotten the way
you took advantage
of Emperor Beld?
[KASHUE]
I have no excuses to offer.
But at the time,
there was no other way.
And yet, you dare to call
yourself a man of honor.
You broke the rules of combat,
and you feel no shame?
Please, Sir Ashram,
what are you talking about?
It was five years ago.
He was fighting
Beld in the War of Heroes.
[KASHUE panting]
[ASHRAM] They were engaged
in single combat,
when someone launched an arrow,
striking Emperor Beld
in the arm.
[BELD gasps]
[yells]
In a brazen act of cowardice,
he took advantage of the
moment to win the fight.
The fate of Lodoss was in
my hands; I had no choice.
If I had not won that
sword fight with Beld,
then Marmo certainly
would have won the war.
But what--what are you saying?!
Will the god of war
condemn me for that?
Will Myrii curse my
name as a knight
for having saved all of Lodoss?!
[HOBB]
Um, well, uh... I, uh...
[PARN]
King Kashue!
[KASHUE]
Parn!
There's no need for you to make
any deals with them,
Your Highness.
My team has already
taken care of Ashram's men.
Groder and the
others were beaten?!
Im-Impossible!
Come on, let's finish
these two off.
And then, we can go destroy
Shooting Star by ourselves.
[KASHUE]
Parn!
I will honor the agreement
I have made with Ashram.
It is my duty as
a knight... and as a king.
[PARN gasps]
[KASHUE]
We will kill Shooting Star...
...together!
You heard the agreement?
Yes, I did, sir.
"Let he who breaks this promise
feel the wrath of Myrii!"
Parn!
Deed! Summon the water spirit!
You've got to protect King
Kashue from the dragon's flames!
Leylia! Cast a protection spell!
Right!
And Cecil, I want you
to cover King Kashue!
You don't have to tell me twice!
"Salamander's foot,
breath of efreet,
angry heart of the
ancient titans..."
"Marfa, mother of the Earth.
Protect him from
the demonic fire."
"Spirit of water.
Blessed maiden.
Shield our brave warriors
from the dragon's flames."
Now you will feel the wrath
of all the souls of Flaim
whose lives you destroyed!
--[SHOOTING STAR roars]
--[KASHUE grunts]
"Vanna flame ve igloss!"
[PARN]
Highness!
[ASHRAM yells]
[SHOOTING STAR groans]
[ASHRAM shouts]
Ashram!
His eye!
Yes, I'll distract him.
You get around to
his blind side.
But sir!
There's no time
to hesitate! Now move!
But Your Highness!
Come on, you damned beast!
[yells]
"I summon the power
of the War God Myrii
to ease the pain
and heal the wounds
of this brave warrior."
[ASHRAM groaning]
Sir Ashram!
Sir Ashram, wait!
[KASHUE grunting]
Wow, this is great!
I'm right in the
middle of the action.
What a great
ballad this'll make.
It's no use! The water
spirits are too weak
to function inside this volcano!
"Roar of the demon wolf,
embrace of snow.
Manna of creation!"
[CECIL yells]
"Become a frozen blade of
ice and cut the fire!"
[PARN gasps]
Parn!
[BOTH yelling]
"I summon the
spirit of the Earth.
Mighty beast of
the ground below.
I beg of you, answer my call."
Now!
[BOTH grunt]
[SHOOTING STAR groans]
[SHOOTING STAR]
Curse... you... humans...!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! We won!
[ASHRAM panting]
[PARN panting]
We did it.
Shooting Star is finally dead.
[KASHUE]
Now, Sir Ashram...
Oh, stop them!
They made a deal, Deed.
We can't stop them.
Wait! Please, Sir Ashram!
Let me heal your wounds, sir.
Just start the duel, Hobb.
But sir...
[ASHRAM]
Hobb...!
"Now, in the holy name of Myrii,
let the battle between
these two knights begin."
[BOTH yelling, grunting]
He's hurt.
Deedlit.
But he's hurt!
It's all right.
King Kashue will win.
But what--
There is a code of
honor among men, Deed.
We cannot stop it.
[grunting continues]
Why must the two of you continue
to engage in this
useless fight?!
Both of you are worthy
and heroic men!
Both of you have high ideals!
And both of you give all
you can to realize them!
So why must you do this?!
You're not a better man.
We're both the same!
You and I are not the same!
I am not so much driven by
my ideals as by my duties.
I am the king of Flaim!
To protect my kingdom,
I must risk my life itself!
Unlike you, I cannot
focus on just one goal.
Your ambitions are
a threat to my kingdom,
and that is the
only reason I'm here.
[ASHRAM scoffs]
You're just a foolish man
who's trapped in a king!
Stand back. I'll finish you off!
[PARN]
Highness!
[ASHRAM yelling]
[KASHUE groans]
[grunts]
Why...?
[ASHRAM, KASHUE groan]
Are you all right?
[groaning continues]
How-- How can this be?
[ASHRAM] It can't be...
It can't... It can't!
[KASHUE]
Let this end.
Please, this madness must end.
Why can't I...
Why can I not beat this man?!
[ASHRAM] I must... I must
fulfill Emperor Beld's wishes!
No matter what... I must...
[gasps]
I must...
...no matter what!
[HOBB gasps]
[KASHUE]
Huh?
[PARN]
Wha--? Hey!
[DEEDLIT]
Parn!
Ashram! Have you forgotten
your agreement?!
I won't lose to
the likes of you!
[PARN groans]
[ASHRAM]
With this...
With this, I can finally...!
[ASHRAM yells]
[ASHRAM]
I will unite Lodoss!
[KASHUE]
If you hadn't stopped to think
about the consequences...
...then you might have won.
[yells]
[ASHRAM gasps]
[PARN yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[gasping continues]
[PARN]
Ashram!
All for a united Lodoss...
Emperor Beld's dream...
Ashram! No!
[gasps]
But Your Highness!
Don't stop him.
Ashram is a man of principle.
Only now... he's got
nothing to live for.
Emperor Beld...
For...give... me...
[groans]
[ALL gasp]
[ASHRAM]
My dreams... My dreams...
Ashram... Why did
you have to break
your agreement with King Kashue?
You were such a brave
and noble hero, Ashram.
Or is it I who have been blind?
[KASHUE]
A hero is still only a man.
And when a man pursues
his own desires,
he will sometimes
act without thinking.
I, too, am a coward who
broke his word to someone.
[HOBB]
King Kashue...
I decided to join Ashram
to confirm my own faith.
I wanted to witness true
heroism and true valor
and to discover for myself
the true meaning of war.
When you have found
your answers, Hobb,
I hope you will return to Blade.
My kingdom still needs the
services of a priest of Myrii.
[HOBB]
Y-Yes, sir...
But Hobb, if you really
want to find a true hero...
[CECIL]
Parn!
[MAAR]
You were great!
Nice work, brave knight.
Thank you.
[BOTH laugh]
[KASHUE]
...you need look no further
than the warrior
who walks among us.
[SHIRIS]
So, you won.
[PARN grunts]
[PARN]
I may have won this battle,
but to what end?
I wasn't able to
save Orson's life
or Shiris's heart, either.
Even though I beat my enemies,
my friends' wounds
may never heal.
Even in victory, it seems
there are some losses
that can never be recovered.
[SHIRIS]
Well, let's get going.
[PARN]
Huh?
I can't just stop my life.
I've got to keep going.
And try my best to
make a difference.
My own way.
Shiris...
After all, if Orson saved
my life, I should live it.
Yeah... Yeah, you're right.
Then, let's go.
[SHIRIS]
It's better this way, Orson.
Let's go, Parn.
[PARN]
Mm. Let's go.
Let's go back home!
Now, to the Lodoss we all saved!
[NARRATOR] To the south of
the continent of Alecrast
lies an island known as Lodoss.
And now, etched forever
onto its war-torn history,
is the chronicle of a new hero.
And etched onto the
heart of that hero,
is the eternal joy
of true victory.
[PARN]
Welcome...
...to Lodoss Island!
What you've all
been waiting for...
[BOTH]
...the second part!
[giggles]
[music plays]
Hi, it's great to see you!
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
[BOTH]
DJs Parn and Deedlit are here!
And now, it's time for
"How, What, and Why!"
Time for question number one.
[GIRL VOICE] "Could you explain
how King Kashue beat Ashram?"
That was our first question.
And for the answer,
let's go to Shiris,
our ace field reporter.
Okey-dokey, Shiris.
Take it away!
This is Shiris, coming to
you from castle Akroyd!
We're trying to find out how a
laid-back guy like Kashue, uh...
Uh, how a guy like Kashue
was able to defeat
a dedicated guy like Ashram.
It looks like we may be
close to an answer.
[KASHUE] It wasn't a very
difficult thing to do.
You know I had to beat him.
After all, I am
the king of Flaim!
Yes, but what about Ashram's
famous Soul Crusher,
the demon sword? Weren't you
scared it would beat you?
[KASHUE grunts]
I'll tell you about that sword.
[SHIRIS yelps]
[clears throat] King Kashue,
should I be telling
our quip-happy
audience to get ready?
Yes! For I shall not be gored...
...by just any old demon sword!
[thumping]
[KASHUE whimpering]
Here's our next question!
[GIRL'S VOICE]
"What was the War of Heroes?"
That was a very good question.
Now then, why don't we touch
upon the War of Heroes,
which happened five years ago
between Emperor Beld
and King Fahn.
[BOTH]
Well, we touched it!
[ALL groaning]
Well, that's it for today!
So long for now! Goodbye!
Bye...!
Bye!
[ALL]
We'll be seeing you!
[PARN] Ten years have
passed since the showdown
at Fire Dragon Mountain.
As the time slipped by,
the heroes went
their separate ways.
And, as the history of
Lodoss has shown before,
a young knight is given
a new mission to follow.
Next time,
on Record of Lodoss War:
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"The Young Knight...
Tested Strength."