[DARK ELF A laughing]
[SPARK]
Calm down... Just calm down!
He may be a Dark Elf,
but he's alone!
If it's a one-on-one fight,
even I can handle it!
Careful! He can make himself
disappear with his magic.
But if I can slash him
before he gets the chance,
I can beat this guy!
And if I do, they'll have
to make me a knight!
This is it.
[yells]
[DARK ELF A groans]
I got him! Yeah!
[chanting]
[SPARK]
Oh, no, you don't!
Now, you're mine!
Huh?!
[yelps]
Impossible!
That was a fire spell! Huh?
[DARK ELVES chuckle]
Damn, where did
they all come from?
[SPARK] Five to one?
There's no way I can win.
But what should I do?
What should I do?!
If I turn my back
on them, I'm dead!
But if I don't...
Here goes!
[SPARK yells]
[DARK ELVES gasp]
Help! Help! Intruders!
Intruders in the treasure house!
Help! Come quickly! Intruders--
[SPARK groans]
[DEEDLIT]
Parn! Did you hear that?
Yeah. I think the shouts
came from over here.
I've got a bad feeling...
--[rustling]
--[BOTH gasp]
[SPARK groaning]
[PARN]
Spark?
Spark! What happened?
Tell me, who did this?
D-D-Dark Elves got into
the treasure house...
There were five of them...
Did you see where they went?
Hurry... Seal off the castle!
[groans]
Deed!
On my way.
Come on! Don't die.
Spark! Spark!
Who are you?
Just leave this to me.
"Myrii, Great God of War.
Heal this brave man's wounds."
[GUARD A]
Intruders!
[GUARD B]
Seal the gates!
[GUARD C]
They hit the treasure house!
[GUARD D]
Seal the rear gates as well!
[GUARD E]
Search the castle grounds!
What's going on, Slayn?
I was afraid this would happen.
Highness!
We're searching
the castle grounds,
but there's no sign of them.
That can't me!
We sealed the gates right away.
They must be somewhere
on the castle grounds!
Highness! If they
really were Dark Elves,
they could have made
themselves invisible
and walked right past us.
Shamanist magic!
But what were
they after, Slayn?
The tools...
The Destroyer's tools.
But... What are
you talking about?
[SLAYN]
It has begun...
A new evil is about to
take hold of Lodoss!
[PARN gasps]
[KASHUE]
How is Spark doing?
[GUARD A]
Priest Greevus is administering
a healing spell now.
He told me that
Spark should survive.
[KASHUE] As soon as he is able,
have him report to my chambers.
[GUARD A]
Yes, sir!
Parn and Deedlit,
you'd better come with me.
[KASHUE]
I will explain the situation
to the two of you directly.
But no one else
may know of this.
If our soldiers or
citizens find out,
it would cause
widespread panic in Flaim.
[SLAYN] I will tell you
everything we know.
We've learned that the Marmo
have just embarked
on a terrible plan.
What sort of plan? Tell us.
The resurrection of Kardis.
The Goddess of Destruction?!
But why would anyone wanna
do something like that?
Kardis has been sealed
away for centuries!
Ever since the
creation of Lodoss!
Yes, you're right, Deed.
Kardis was one of the goddesses
responsible for the
creation of Lodoss.
During the War of the Gods,
the forces light fought
against the forces of darkness.
And Marfa, the Goddess
of the Earth,
engaged Kardis the Destroyer
in a ferocious battle
of supreme heroism.
[SLAYN] In the end, Marfa used
her power to seal Kardis away.
But before Marfa could finish,
Kardis put a terrible
curse on the land.
[SLAYN]
Then Marfa,
already mortally
wounded from her battle,
used the last of her strength
to perform a miracle.
[SLAYN]
To save the continent,
she split the cursed
land away from it!
[SLAYN] And that
cursed land... is Lodoss.
But what will they accomplish?
If Kardis comes back,
the whole world will end.
They'd be better off
resurrecting Falaris,
the God of Darkness.
All we can do now is pray that
the Marmo aren't madmen.
So who is behind this?
The dark priests?
The leaders of
the Dark Elf tribe?
No. As far as I know, Parn,
there is only one
person in Marmo
who could actually
make this plan happen.
[DEEDLIT]
You mean...
It can be no one else but him!
[WAGNARD] "Nadeera...
Nani iru vey Kardis...
Ana adaru nees..."
It shall come!
Oh, it shall come!
The time of your
resurrection is near.
And the Destroyer's tools
that were stolen, Slayn.
They have something to do
with Kardis's resurrection?
Yes. "Two keys, one door, and
Kardis shall awaken once more."
[PARN]
Is that some old legend?
[SLAYN]
The two keys are the two tools.
The one door is a live sacrifice
for the advent of Kardis.
When these three things
are brought together,
Kardis is reborn.
The Dark Elves
stole one of them.
It was the Soul Crystal Ball.
The Soul Crystal Ball?
That's what we recovered after
we won the battle with Ashram!
When the battle was over,
I took it from Maar and stored
it in the treasure house.
And what is the
other tool, Slayn?
It is called the Staff of Life.
And it is stored in
the temple of Falis.
That's their next target!
Calm down, Parn.
We will attack the
Marmo and stop them.
--[PARN] But--
--Don't worry.
I'll send a
dispatch to warn Valis.
King Etoh will be able to
provide additional protection
for the Staff of Life.
Leave the right job
to the right people.
The king is right. We can trust
Etoh to handle this, Parn.
I'm ordering a pursuit
team out after them.
If my men can retrieve
the Soul Crystal Ball,
then there will be
nothing to worry about.
In that case, Highness,
I have a favor to ask.
[KASHUE]
Hm?
[SPARK] It's Spark, Your
Highness. Reporting as ordered.
Enter!
[KASHUE]
Why, Spark?
Why didn't you sound
the alarm immediately?
[SPARK]
I beg your pardon, Highness?
Why did you wait
to sound the alarm?!
I thought-- I thought that
I could beat him myself.
If I beat him,
it would've proven to you
that I was ready to be a knight.
That's what I thought, anyway...
I fully expect to be punished.
And you shall.
You are to join the pursuit.
Wait in the guard
room for my orders.
[MAN A] Did you hear? It sounds
like a big battle is brewing.
[MAN B] The king is ready for
a showdown with the Marmo.
I haven't seen any fighting
in almost ten years.
I was beginning to think I
might never go to war again.
[MAN C]
I know what you mean.
I heard those
intruders last night
were actually Marmo agents.
[MAN D] Yeah, and they
got away with some
valuable treasure, too!
Those guards
must've been asleep!
They should've called for help--
[CAPTAIN]
Quiet down, men!
[gasps]
Here are your assignments.
Listen up!
Sir Farus, report to
Fortress 12 in the west!
Sir!
[CAPTAIN]
Sir Bohnu and Sir Dagral
will go to Fortress 18
in the north.
[BOTH]
Sir!
[CAPTAIN]
Sir Tahgi and Sir Rudolf,
Fortress 8 in the east!
[BOTH]
Sir!
[ALDO] None of the other
treasures were even touched.
The only thing they took
was the Soul Crystal Ball...
[ALDO]
And even though Slayn
cast a strong
protection spell on it,
they managed to steal the
crystal with no effort at all.
[SLAYN]
It seems the intruders had
a powerful sorcerer among them.
[ALDO]
Master Slayn!
I beg your forgiveness,
Master Slayn.
Securing this place
was my responsibility.
Stop. This was not
your fault, Aldonova.
I was the one who cast
the protection spell here.
If someone
deserves blame, it is I.
But sir, the door.
What about the door?
The door is safe.
Thank goodness...
Then you must allow me to
protect the door, Master,
even with my li--
While I appreciate
your intentions,
I cannot allow it.
But why, Master?
[SLAYN]
Because, Aldonova,
I have a different
favor to ask of you.
[CAPTAIN] Sir Carlberos, report
to Fortress 6 in the south.
Sir!
[SPARK]
But Captain, wait! Please!
[CAPTAIN]
What?!
Uh... Please, sir, you forgot
about my assignment.
[CAPTAIN]
Your assignment?!
[SPARK] The king ordered
me to wait here until
he decided what my
assignment would be!
[CAPTAIN] Well, I haven't
heard anything about it.
[SPARK]
I see, sir...
[door opens, closes]
[sighs]
[growls]
[knocking]
[SPARK]
Huh?
[GARRACK] I'm looking for an
idiot gloryhound named Spark,
the guy who let
the intruders escape.
I happen to be that idiot.
I just got my orders
from Lord Shadam.
As of today, you are my captain.
I'm a mercenary,
and Garrack is my name.
Because of this thing here,
most people call me
the Blue Meteor.
You can if you want.
Well, whatever the case,
it's good to meet you.
Hold on there! What do you mean?
Your captain? Is this-- Hey!
I'm supposed to be
under punishment!
Don't joke around!
E-Ease up! Just calm down!
[LEAF]
Oh no! Don't tell me
I'm hooked up with
you again, Garrack.
[GARRACK gasps]
Leaf!
Oh, man! I knew there was
something wrong with this job!
I should be saying
the same thing!
[SPARK growling]
Hey! This is no place
for a woman or a child!
[LEAF]
Oh.
[yelps]
[LEAF]
Outta my way, pal!
So, Garrack, you know
who our captain is?
[GARRACK]
Uh...
[LEAF]
Huh?
You're kidding, right?
Hey, do you think I
should apologize to him?
I think you know the game.
Or at least you should by now.
If you make a good impression,
you know you'll get paid.
Why you... What did
you do that for?!
Oh, forgive me. Um, I had no
idea you were the captain here.
Uh, my name is Leaf,
and I'm a Half-Elf.
I'm a mercenary,
just like Garrack here.
How do you do?
[gasps]
[SPARK groaning]
[LEAF]
Some captain...
[PARN]
Is Spark in here?
[SPARK] Another one?
Just great... Now who wants--
[gasps]
[SPARK]
H-Highness!
Are you ready to
receive your orders?
[SPARK]
Yes, sir!
You shall deliver this dispatch
to King Etoh of Valis.
You are to leave at once.
[SPARK]
Huh?
Now listen carefully.
We've received word that the
intruders from last night
have fled to the
south toward Valis.
I have chosen a special pursuit
team that you will command.
Your mission is to recover
the stolen treasure,
the Soul Crystal Ball.
Huh?
Highness, does this mean my
honor has been restored?
Don't get too hasty, Spark!
The kingdom of Flaim
is in a state of war,
and you are still a
knight in training.
I do not expect
you to return here
until your mission is complete.
Yes, sir!
You can count on me!
[DEEDLIT giggles]
[SPARK]
Huh?
Priest Greevus!
Here, kid, you forgot something.
You can't expect to go
on a mission without it.
Thank you, sir!
Ah... My sword.
Your Highness, I'd like
to ask your permission
--to accompany them.
--[GROUP gasps]
Greevus... It's all right
with me, but why?
Because I like this kid.
Do I really need a reason?
He left his sword behind while
he was trying to
escape the enemy.
In my mind, that takes a
special kind of courage.
Greevus...
Even the bravest of knights
forgets that a sword is a tool.
Some even value their sword
more than their own lives.
But the God of War has taught me
a different standard of courage.
Isn't that right, Miss?
[DEEDLIT]
Huh? Hmph.
Are you sure, sir?
It's all right.
My faith in the
God of War is all
that I need to ensure my safety.
Highness, is this everyone
who will be coming along?
[KASHUE]
One more will be coming as well.
It looks like he's late.
Then there's time.
Will you come with me
for a while, Spark?
Yes, sir! I don't mind, but--
[PARN]
Okay, this way.
Y-Yes.
[SPARK]
W-Why are we here?
Catch!
Huh? Uh...
But what do you want to--
I didn't come here
to talk to you.
I wanted to test
your skills, Spark.
[SPARK]
Huh?
[PARN] King Kashue says
you've gotten pretty good.
No, not really.
[PARN] Perhaps I'm not
good enough for you?
[SPARK]
N-No, sir! This is an honor!
Getting to match
swords with you,
the great free knight is, well--
It's a dream come true, sir!
Well then, shall we begin?
Yes!
[PARN yells]
[SPARK yelps]
When you cross swords,
nothing can distract you.
If this were a battle,
you'd already be dead!
Y-Yes, sir!
[yells]
A predictable charge.
Watch your opponent's moves!
Then predict his next one!
You must think
before you attack.
You can never win
with just raw strength.
Right, sir!
[yells]
Keep on maneuvering until you
can really get a clean shot.
[PARN] Just what I'd
expect from someone
King Kashue has high hopes for.
The kid is good.
I'll never forget what
you taught me today.
Thank you so much, Sir Parn!
Good luck and stay safe.
Yes, sir! I will never abandon
my duties like I did last night.
The error was unforgivable.
Don't do that, either.
Don't do that? But why--
It's wrong to abandon yourself.
Don't become a man
who lives only
for the duty
that's given to him.
Huh?
You'll understand someday.
Ahh, Captain! Our last
member has arrived!
[SPARK]
Huh?
Forgive me for being late.
My name is Aldonova.
I am at your service,
Master Spark.
Just call me Spark, please.
Excuse me, the intruders
have been sighted
near Fortress 18 in the south!
Master Spark, you've got
to move out at once!
Understood!
We'll leave right now!
[KASHUE] I hope you're
right about this, Parn.
For better or for worse,
battle changes people.
I think this will
do him some good.
He has no idea that
the thing he seeks
will change the
future of Lodoss.
Perhaps it's better that way.
King Kashue, Kanon awaits us,
but we wish you
luck against the Marmo.
[KASHUE] Thanks.
And let us meet again soon.
And so, the fate of Lodoss
is placed once again
in the hands of one so young,
yet so full of promise.
[PARN, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've
been waiting for,
the second part!
Ha-ha!
I am Spark!
Knight of Flaim, Spark!
But I'm still just
one in training.
What are you doing
over there, Spark?
I'm gonna leave you behind!
Yeah, yeah. I'm coming.
I know this is supposed to give
me experience as a knight,
but delivering cookies?!
What are you saying, Spark?
Guarding people is an
important job for a knight!
Yeah, I guess so.
[SPARK] First of all,
who would attack us
over some lousy cookies?
I don't think protecting baked
goods is valuable experience.
[gasps, yelps]
Spark!
I-I-I-I thought I was gonna die!
[DARK ELF laughs] Hey,
so you're the young champion
who's, uh, guarding the
young lady here, huh?
Who's there?!
I've been waiting
for you there, Neese!
You must be...
The Dark Elf with a sweet tooth!
Oh! Did you say Dark Elf?!
[DARK ELF] Now legend
has it there that, uh,
all the cookies baked in
the temple of Marfa there
have a taste that's
beyond compare!
Now let's have 'em!
Huh?!
[NEESE]
Oh, what a terrible thing!
Are you sure you're okay?
[SPARK]
Yeah, I think so.
[DARK ELF]
Hold it, hold it, hold it there!
You're supposed to listen
to me when I talk to you.
If you insult me again,
you'll taste my wrath!
[NEESE yelps]
[SPARK]
Hey!
[NEESE]
Huh?
[DARK ELF]
Ouch, huh.
Oh, thanks so much,
little dragon!
[dragon purrs]
[NEESE]
Okay, let's go!
[SPARK] I've got such a bad
feeling about what's ahead...
[ALL]
We'll be seeing you!
[SPARK] Pursuing our enemies,
we find ourselves
caught in a terrible trap
set by the Dark Elves!
An enormous monster
attacks the fortress!
And, as I face my
first real battle,
a lone girl appears
in a burst of light!
Next time,
on Record of Lodoss War:
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"Light... A Girl
Guided by the Gods."