[NARRATOR] It has been two days
since Orson and his comrades
were defeated by Ashram
at the pirates' hideaway.
Now captives, they are on their
way to Blue Dragon Island
aboard the Marmo military ship,
Sea Devil's Horn.
[ASHRAM] I see. I figured
they were sent from Flaim.
And with a berserker among
them... You're sure?
I sense the spirit's within him.
The spirit of anger
is most strong, indeed.
Hyuri can blaze to life
like burning hot lava.
Fascinating.
And you're saying that
there's no way he can
consciously control his
berserker strength?
[ASTAR]
Impossible.
I see.
[ORSON] Except for the time
I felt the spirit of anger
releasing me from its spell.
I called it back because I
needed its power to fight.
Can it be that I don't really
want to escape Hyuri's spell?
Orson...
[door opens]
[SHIRIS]
Orson!
Sorry about that.
Why you!
Shiris, you're too
weak to try to move.
I'm all right.
Lucky for you, I got a
little careless before.
You won't beat me again.
I swear it!
Oh, yeah? I'll take you
on any time, little girl.
Damn!
Shiris...
I'll beat her! I swear it!
[ORSON] Shiris, there's no way
you can beat that warrior.
You'll lose. You'll lose
every single time.
Back off! She's nothing
but a big brute!
In an honest sword fight,
there's no way she
would ever beat me!
[ORSON] In a strict test
of swordsmanship,
you probably would win.
But real battle is different,
and you know it.
Just drop it!
It's just like trying
to say you could beat me.
While you might be
able to hurt me,
I would be the one to
score the lethal wound.
I said drop it! Come on!
You're way outta
line on this, Orson!
Next time, I won't lose!
And it's not for the sake
of Lodoss or Parn or--
It's for the sake
of my own pride!
I have to beat that woman!
[ORSON]
I'm sorry, Shiris.
I wasn't strong
enough, either...
Orson! You're crying!
Can it be that you've
learned how to feel again?
[NARRATOR] The Sea Devil's
Horn finally arrives
at Blue Dragon Island,
home of Abram the sea dragon.
At once, Ashram and
his group set out
to acquire the Scepter
of Domination,
the greatest of the
Governor's Treasures.
In order to have a living
witness to his greatest triumph,
Ashram has decided
to bring Orson along.
[HOBB] I hope Abram holds
the Scepter of Domination.
If he does, then your
journey will end
right here at Blue
Dragon Island.
You're wrong.
Once I possess the
Scepter of Domination,
our true battle will begin.
The battle to unite
Lodoss awaits us all.
Look there!
[ORSON]
That's Abram, the sea dragon!
[ASHRAM]
Let's go!
A moment, sir.
I would like to try
to negotiate with him.
[ASHRAM]
Negotiate?!
Yes, sir.
Very well.
[GRODER]
Thank you, sir.
I dare say, that if we can get
the scepter without a fight,
then nothing will
stand in our way.
Who dares to disturb
my slumber?
A human.
I could tell you my name,
but it would mean
nothing to you.
I have no use for puny,
little human beings.
I suggest you leave now.
I wish to sleep.
Abram, I have a
question for you.
Is it true that you guard
the Scepter of Domination?
I do not. Now leave!
Then... what about the
Soul Crystal Ball?
[ABRAM]
I do indeed possess that.
[GRODER] Master Wagnard,
the search is over at last!
I've found the
Soul Crystal Ball!
Human! If you think
that you can succeed
in stealing from me,
prepare, for you will die!
[GRODER] No, Abram.
It is you who will die today.
[ABRAM]
We shall see about that!
[roars]
I assume he said no.
That's right, sir.
And I'm sure that Abram does
not possess the scepter.
Hmph!
But he's angry with us
for disturbing his sleep.
Now he wants to devour us.
Then we must fight.
The berserker can stay behind.
[gasps]
Let's go!
Sing the song of battle!
The dragon's roar can shatter
even a warrior's resolve.
Protect us from it!
By your command!
[singing]
[ORSON] I... I'm scared.
I want... I want to run.
Can this be... fear?!
[ASHRAM]
Move out!
"I call forth the power
of the mighty kraken!"
[NARRATOR]
Abram's movements were dulled
by his recent hibernation.
He breathed fire,
thrashed his mighty tail,
and fought against the onslaught
of magical lightning attacks.
But in the end,
Abram could not withstand
the relentless attacks of
Ashram and his fighters.
Until finally...
[yells]
[ORSON]
Wha-- What are you doing to me?
[HOBB] "Myrii, give peace
to this man's heart."
You'll be all right.
[ORSON]
Y-You won?
We did somehow.
And yet, there was
no point to this fight.
What is that thing, Groder?
Sir, this is the
Soul Crystal Ball.
Another of the
Governor's Treasures.
The Soul Crystal Ball...
It's used to summon the
souls of the dead, isn't it?
We still haven't studied it,
so I cannot give you
a definite answer.
You look quite happy, Groder.
Does it not upset you
that I must now do battle
with Shooting Star as well?
Please forgive my poor manners.
But I just cannot wait
to begin my study
of this most fascinating object.
Hm. We must set out for Flaim.
Then to Fire Dragon Mountain.
We cannot let Kashue
beat us there!
Master Wagnard! Master Wagnard!
It is time for us
to rejoice, my lord!
I have secured the
Soul Crystal Ball!
[WAGNARD]
You've done it, Groder!
Now all that remains
is to return
the Soul Crystal Ball
safely to me.
[GRODER]
Yes, sir.
[WAGNARD]
Now you must avoid all risks.
Above all, you must not
fight Shooting Star!
He is the strongest and
most deadly dragon there is.
I doubt even Ashram
can defeat him.
In any case, you've done well.
Come back to me at once!
What does he think I am?
After I risk my life to
get the Soul Crystal Ball,
now he will want
to dispose of me?
[knocking]
[MARMO A]
Master Groder,
Sir Ashram needs to
see you immediately.
[GRODER]
Very well. I'll come at once.
Why are you looking at me?
He's changed. Something's wrong.
Then-- Then this
must mean that he's...
Orson, I think you're cured!
You've got your feelings back!
Y-You really think so?
I don't understand why, but--
That look on your face?
And in your eyes?
It's definite; you're cured!
Yes! Now we have to
escape no matter what!
That's something for our
leader to decide. Right?
Uh... Yeah!
Let's think of a plan.
When we go,
we'll all go together!
[SHIRIS]
Right, Leader!
[MAAR] Well, I'm gonna try
to escape on my own!
[snickers]
[NARRATOR] While Orson and
the others plan their escape,
Slayn and Leylia pay a
visit to Captain Genner,
chief of Raiden's
defense forces.
After explaining the situation,
they ask that a rescue party
be sent out to save
their comrades.
I understand your worries,
and I wish there was
something I could do,
but I cannot spare any troops.
I understand.
I suppose we have no choice but
to go after them on our own.
No, dear, we wouldn't
stand a chance
without the proper
fighter support.
Magic alone is not enough.
[door opens]
[PARN] Is someone looking
for fighter support?
[DEEDLIT] I know three
warriors who can help you out.
Parn!
You know, you should be quieter
when discussing your secrets.
Your voice carries quite a ways.
[SHIRIS]
Hm?
Is everybody ready?
I'll draw him in,
and you guys jump him.
[door opens]
All right! Got your food here!
[CECIL]
Shiris... Be careful.
It took you long enough!
What kept you?
Shut up! You should be happy
we're feeding you at all.
[MAAR] "Pixies of rest,
spirits of sleep. Send..."
What? What the--?
[MAAR] "And send him
to the land of dreams.
Silence, darkness,
quiet death..."
[CECIL]
That's-- That's Low Ancient!
[SHIRIS] Don't tell me
he's chanting a spell!
[ORSON]
M-Maar... Ugh...
[MAAR]
"Oblivion. Peace of mind.
Mime Rime Alreem...
Silence, darkness,
take on new life.
Leera Medeera Ru..."
Nothing personal, guys.
[MAAR]
Uh-oh! Somebody's coming!
Oh, Ganeed, god of thieves!
Please let nobody be in here!
[MAAR]
Huh?
[snickers]
[PIRATE A] Help! One of the
prisoners has escaped!
You're too late!
How could you let
them escape?! How?!
Uh, it was just the child.
[ASTAR]
No... It was a grass runner.
Let him go.
What the--?!
[GRODER] The grass runner
wouldn't have stolen it...
...or would he?
[roaring]
What's up there?
It looks like a
grass runner, Parn.
[PARN]
What's a grass runner?
[DEEDLIT] Grass runners
are meadow sprites.
They come from the realm
of the plant fairies,
just like elves.
That must be Maar.
He looks like he's all right.
[MAAR]
Ee! Oh no!
I give up.
[DEEDLIT] Thank goodness
everyone's still alive.
[MAAR]
Thanks. It feels better now.
Enough of that!
Now tell me how it can be that
you were the only one to escape.
This is no time to be asking
a question like that.
But we're in luck
since he can guide us
right back to the
pirates' hideout.
Huh?! Uh, no way! Those guys are
tough! They're gonna kill me!
They won't beat us, Maar.
Because we'll be
fighting alongside
the great mercenary king.
King Kashue of Flaim?
Is it true?
[PARN]
It is. So will you be our guide?
Sure. I will.
[PIRATE B]
Enemy attack!
[PARN, KASHUE yelling]
"Salamander's foot,
breath of efreet!
Angry heart of the
ancient titans...
Manna of all creation,
become the fires of destruction!
Vanna flame ve igloss!"
Don't run! Fight!
[gasps]
[yells]
Tell me, what are
you Marmo doing?
But I'm not Marmo. I'm just
the captain of the ship.
And besides,
who the hell are you?!
My name, perhaps
you've heard of it.
I'm Kashue Arnegue the Third.
What?! But you're
the king of Flaim!
Something mighty big
must be happening
if you decided to come here!
Talk! Where are Ashram
and the others?
They-- They went to
Fire Dragon Mountain!
That's what he told me.
Are Orson and the
others all right?
[CAPTAIN]
Of course they are!
I wonder what's going on.
Calm down! Orson!
Sorry for the delay, Orson.
[ALL]
Parn!
Is everyone all right?
[SHIRIS]
Oh, Parn!
[DEEDLIT grunts]
[PARN]
Shiris! What happened to you?
[SHIRIS] Oh, I'm fine!
It's nothing major.
What are you doing here?
We were just about to
launch our escape plan.
Just as I figured. But since
we're in such a hurry,
I thought we might
help speed things up.
Yeah? Well, that's okay.
Parn, I don't know
how to thank you!
Orson?
It looks like the power
of the spirit of anger
has grown much weaker in him.
He's got his emotions back.
[CECIL] Maar! How could
you betray us like that?!
[MAAR]
I'm sorry!
It was the only thing
I could do at the time!
[SHIRIS]
So, what's next for us?
We head straight for
Fire Dragon Mountain.
Ashram must never be allowed to
get the Scepter of Domination.
I'm going, too!
Are you sure?
It looks to me like you
could use some rest.
I'm definitely going!
I've got some unfinished
business to settle
with one of them!
All right.
[CECIL]
I'm coming, too.
I must restore my good name.
And I'm coming along, too!
Very well. You're all
welcome to come.
This way, we can take
care of Ashram
and Shooting Star
at the same time.
[ALL]
Huh?
[PARN]
Wh-What's happened to the sky?!
It's nighttime, but it's
suddenly as bright as day!
Could it be that the whole
city of Raiden is on fire?!
[SLAYN]
Oh, that it were not true...
[DEEDLIT] He said he'd kill
a hundred people
for every scale we scratched.
Shooting Star is
attacking the city!
We must get back
to Raiden right now!
There's nothing we can do.
But-- If we do nothing,
the people of Raiden will--
[KASHUE]
Don't say it, Parn!
Don't you think I'm
aware of that myself?
But putting a stop to Ashram's
ambitions must come first.
It's tough, but sometimes a king
must make the tough decisions.
But they'll--
You know this must hurt
King Kashue as well.
But a king must consider
the lives of all,
not just the lives of a few.
For now, we must concentrate our
efforts on our main objective.
We must put a stop to this,
once and for all.
Very well, Slayn.
Now we must all go to do our
jobs at Fire Dragon Mountain.
[PARN] We must get the
Scepter of Domination,
and put an end to
Ashram's ambitions forever!
--Welcome...
--...to Lodoss Island!
What you've all
been waiting for...
...the second part!
[giggles]
We wouldn't stand a chance
without the proper
fighter support.
Magic alone is not enough.
[PARN] Did somebody say
they needed fighter support?
Yeah? That's gotta be Parn!
[PARN] Sorry, but I've
become a Shamanist,
so I really can't
support you now!
[giggles]
Now, Orson's got
his emotions back,
so we really must be
getting out of here!
That's what I'd
like to do, but...
Whee! We're on a boat!
Hooray, hooray, hooray!
What's he got to
be happy about?!
Yeah, he's acting
like he's a little kid.
Be careful or you're
gonna hurt yourself!
Ow! It hurts!
It hurts, Shiris! Ow!
There, there. It's all
better now, isn't it?
Ooh, Mama, I want some milk.
[SHIRIS]
Huh?!
No way!
[ORSON]
I didn't think it would work...
[roaring]
Oh, no! Raiden is burning up!
We've got to do something! Now!
[KASHUE]
It would do no good.
But if we don't do something,
then Raiden will--
Please don't say it!
Not in that costume!
[PARN giggles]
[DEEDLIT]
How can you act like that...
...at a time like this?!
[NARRATOR] And so,
Parn and his heroic friends
turn their backs on the
burning city of Raiden.
Are you sure you're doing
the right thing, Parn?
I guess so!
If it means I can dress up
like Shiris the next time!
[ALL groan]
[PARN]
Huh?
[growls]
[giggles]
[ALL]
We'll be seeing you!
[SHIRIS] A desperate battle
begins at Fire Dragon Mountain
with the Scepter of
Domination as the prize!
Swords clash,
and shamanist magic makes
the earth below tremble.
It is then that Orson sees
the true spirit of anger
that dwells within people.
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War:
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"Death... A Gentle
Heart Bequeathed."