[NARRATOR]
Light and darkness...
The final battle of the gods
climaxed in a clash between
Marfa, goddess of all creation,
and Kardis, goddess
of destruction.
At the end of their
fierce battle,
the stricken goddesses
had split the continent,
forming a new land.
Since then, people have come
to call this new continent
"Lodoss - The Accursed Island."
The way that you
embrace me with your
strong and powerful arms
Your haunting words keep me
close to everything about you
Romantic in ways
in ways that almost
tear upon my heart
Can't let you go
Don't you know?
Io sono prigioniera
A captive in
your gentle hands
A prisoner of
your soulful eyes,
your special smile
will never part
If the morning sun
should free me
It really wouldn't let me go
I'd still be caught
inside your love
Can't rise above
the chains of your heart
[thunder rumbles, cracks]
Do you think it'll rain?
[CAPTAIN]
I sure hope so...
[thunder rumbles]
[clattering]
[CAPTAIN]
Huh?
[screams]
--Oh! It's him!
--Here he comes!
Attack!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Where the devil
were our guards?!
It's coming here.
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[screams]
[PARN gasps]
Parn, stop!
[KASHUE] Wait! It's too
dangerous to go out!
--[sizzling]
--[PARN groans]
Yaah!
[SHOOTING STAR screeches]
[DEEDLIT]
Parn!
[thunder cracks]
--[PARN sighs]
--[DEEDLIT] Parn...
[SHOOTING STAR growls]
[PIROTESS]
Wait.
We're only after the Scepter
of Domination, right?
It will be mine, once I defeat
the ancient fire dragon.
You mean...?
This sword calls
for the beast's blood.
[PIROTESS] And for that,
you will first need
to possess the scepter.
[ASHRAM]
You doubt my abilities.
[PIROTESS]
But--
Stand aside.
Only foolish humans or goblins
embark on hopeless battles.
--"Hopeless"?
--Do not underestimate
the might of
the ancient dragon.
A mere scratch
could prove to be fatal.
It would serve you well
to remember that.
[gasps]
Parn!
This could've been much worse.
But, recklessness
is your virtue.
Anyway, I've got a feeling that
dragon was only toying with us.
It's like we were
just worms to it.
[DEEDLIT]
Worms have lives, too.
It makes no difference;
a person's life
or a worm's life.
A life is a life.
Deedlit...
[WAGNARD] You allowed the
High Elf to escape?!
[DARK ELF A]
Forgive me, my lord.
[WAGNARD]
And what of Pirotess?
[DARK ELF A]
Well, she's...
[WAGNARD] Gone to
Fire Dragon Mountain.
A Dark Elf in name,
but a woman all the same.
And you have the gall
to return before me?
[gasps]
"Baylos, almighty power of
fiery destruction, come forth.
Baylos, almighty power of
fiery destruction, come forth!"
[DARK ELF A]
Please! Lord Wagnard!
[screams]
[WAGNARD] So now I'll have
the Scepter of Domination
before the sacrifice
of the High Elf.
The "Dragon's Path"?
[ORSON] It sounds
like an old legend.
Yes. In Flaim lore, there is
the ancient legend
of the Dragon Slayer.
At the end of the Dragon's
Path supposedly lies
the dragon's fortress.
I get it. It's a back door
to Shooting Star's lair.
Right, Shadam?
Exactly. In the past,
many warriors set out
with the dream of becoming
the Dragon Slayer.
But none have ever returned.
It's a gamble.
Indeed, but I can see
no other way for us.
What do all of you think?
It's risky.
It's definitely risky,
but not suicidal.
There is another
part of the legend.
[clanging]
[SHADAM] Three lances possessed
by Myrii, the God of War.
They'll help us to seal
the dragon's evil.
The priests are forging
the lances of Myrii
even as we speak.
Very well. We must set out as
soon as they're finished.
King Kashue! You must
let me come with you!
[gasps]
--You really want to?
--Y-Yes, sir.
All right, but no reckless
heroics like before.
You will obey my orders,
is that understood?
Ah... Ah... Yes, sir.
[chuckles]
Oh, Slayn. I fear the
situation is much worse
than I had first imagined.
You mean that Lodoss...
[NEESE]
...faces a grave ordeal.
[LEYLIA]
Mother...
[NEESE] Your powers
will be necessary.
Count on me for help.
I shall help you, too.
[SLAYN]
Leylia.
Dearest Slayn, take care
of my daughter.
[NEESE]
Marfa... Give us strength.
[SHOOTING STAR growls lowly]
[PIROTESS]
Now is the time.
Take me with you.
[ASHRAM]
And if you get in my way...?
Then kill me.
[ASHRAM]
As you wish.
Let's go.
So this is the Dragon's Path...
Your Highness, take this.
[KASHUE] With faith in
Myrii's divine protection
and in your own power,
may you bury yourself
into the creature's heart
inflicting a fatal wound!
Shadam, I leave
the rest to you.
[SHADAM]
Yes, sir!
Grant him a safe return.
Let's go.
The tunnel splits off.
--I'll check it out.
--Wait!
You see what I mean, Parn?
The obvious path
is often the wrong path.
[SHIRIS]
Meaning we go this way.
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[KASHUE] Don't touch it!
You'll be burned!
Shiris!
"Sylph, spirit of the wind.
Let thy powerful forces
protect us from flames."
Quickly now! Come on!
Deedlit!
[DEEDLIT grunt]
Huh?
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Come on!
Don't even think about
trying to fight that beast!
[SHOOTING STAR roars]
Ah... Is that...?
[ALL gasp]
--[WIZARD] Wait.
--[ASHRAM] Hmph.
"Divine power, buried
since ancient times,
open your portal and
allow your master through.
Divine power, buried
since ancient times,
open your portal and
allow your master through.
Divine power, buried
since ancient times,
open your portal and
allow your master through."
[roars]
Highness... It must be!
[gasps]
[SHIRIS]
We're here.
The beast is hungry for blood.
[gasps]
Deedlit? What's the matter?
I see someone.
[ASHRAM] And odd place to meet,
is it not, Mercenary King?
[KASHUE]
Huh?
It's Ashram!
[PARN]
Ashram, you beast!
[KASHUE]
Wait!
That little pup from before...
[PARN]
What're you up to?!
What if I said
"to own all of Lodoss?"
What?!
And look who
came to me this time.
Look, it's her!
[SWORDSMEN growling]
[yells]
Yah!
[chuckles]
[yells]
[SHIRIS]
Eeyah!
[SWORDSMAN A groans]
[ASHRAM chuckles]
You've improved.
[yells]
Didn't you say that
a sword... is not a toy?!
[ASHRAM]
Hmph.
[PARN grunts]
[grunts]
But still so easy.
[roars]
[gasps]
[gasps, screams]
Ashram, save yourself!
[gasps]
That's some fire!
[ASHRAM] I see...
The Scepter of Domination
controls the dragon as well.
What is that?!
It's the Scepter
of Domination!
[ASHRAM]
Impossible!
Parn! The Marmo
can't have that!
What?!
Dragon Slayer, huh?
[growls]
I shall be the one
to defeat the beast!
[snarls]
--Stand aside!
--No! No, it's impossible!
[screams]
[ASHRAM]
Huh?!
The Scepter of Domination
is ours at last!
Aah!
[SHOOTING STAR roars]
[ORSON yells]
[roars]
--Let's do it, Parn!
--[PARN] Right!
[BOTH yell]
It's not safe!
"Sylph, spirit of wind,
protect them."
[roars]
[BOTH yell]
[ASHRAM groans]
Huh...?
[PIROTESS grunts]
[PIROTESS groans]
For the conquest
of Lodoss, my lord.
[gasps]
Pirotess...
[sighs]
[chimes]
We've got to get outta here!
Hurry, Parn!
[NARRATOR] First
encountered amidst flame,
Ashram vanishes amidst flame.
Their meetings were marked more
by the crossing of swords
than by the exchange of words.
Yet Ashram's silent death
has etched itself
upon Parn's heart.
Let all the wonders
come to me
The fantasy fills,
fills my heart
I'll never wander anymore
For all the love I have,
I have for you
All the spirits of the wind
Spread their magic
wings and fly
Racing at the speed of light
Through the valleys
and the passages of time
When we fell in love
Destiny
Now each night
will have no end
Our nights will never end
Eternity awaits
You and me
Now that you are here
We'll never be alone again
Stay with me, my love