[NARRATOR]
Light and darkness...
The final battle of the gods
climaxed in a clash between
Marfa, goddess of all creation,
and Kardis, goddess
of destruction.
At the end of their
fierce battle,
the stricken goddesses
had split the continent,
forming a new land.
Since then, people have come
to call this new continent
"Lodoss - The Accursed Island."
The way that you
embrace me with your
strong and powerful arms
Your haunting words keep me
close to everything about you
Romantic in ways
in ways that almost
tear upon my heart
Can't let you go
Don't you know?
Io sono prigioniera
A captive in
your gentle hands
A prisoner of
your soulful eyes,
your special smile
will never part
If the morning sun
should free me
It really wouldn't let me go
I'd still be caught
inside your love
Can't rise above
the chains of your heart
[NARRATOR] Having lost its
king in the War of Heroes,
Marmo has been reduced
to chaos and turmoil.
With their controlling
spells now broken,
the monsters have reverted
back to wild beasts,
caught in an endless
struggle of survival.
There is no order of any kind.
The mood of the dark island has
become as menacing as its name.
[PIROTESS]
A sacrifice?
[WAGNARD] So young a ruler
in Lodoss is no match
for the power that sleeps
beneath the earth.
[PIROTESS]
You mean Kardis, don't you?
To call forth the infinite
power that awaits us,
a High Elf's life
must be offered.
Do you think your precious
Ashram can conquer Lodoss
with the way
things stand right now?
[thunder cracks]
[roaring]
[yells]
[grunts]
[pants]
[WAGNARD] Can you really
master it in time?
Is the demon sword
"Soul Crusher,"
that has been bathed
in the demon's own blood,
really so easy to handle?
What are you saying?
He who holds
the sword rules Marmo,
he that holds the Scepter of
Domination rules all Lodoss.
Far to the south is a volcano
called Fire Dragon Mountain.
Shooting Star, the demon
dragon who dwells there,
was entrusted with
the scepter by the Ancients.
But, something like that--
Is vital to the
conquest of Lodoss!
[grunts]
He who holds the Scepter of
Domination rules Lodoss.
You should
remember that, Ashram.
It will be mine!
[thunder cracks]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[swords clashing]
[panting]
[yelling continues]
[PARN yells]
[yells]
[gasps]
[DEEDLIT]
Parn!
Highness, it's just
too much for him!
Enthusiasm is a
commendable quality,
however, recklessness is not.
Ah. I'm so sorry...
[MESSENGER]
Highness!
I bring news for
King Kashue of Flaim!
[groans]
Well? What is it?
King Kashue!
It's... Shooting Star!
What?!
[shrieks]
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[screaming continues]
[SHOOTING STAR roars]
[gasps]
[knocking]
[SLAYN]
Come in.
[SLAYN] The robes of a priestess
of Marfa. They suit you.
You think so?
[SLAYN] Now Ghim will
surely rest in peace.
But now I must--
[LEYLIA] Slayn,
are you going somewhere?
[SLAYN]
I don't know.
But... But something
inside is telling me
there is still more distance
to cover on our journey.
[gasps]
[PARN]
King Kashue, please!
[KASHUE]
Didn't I say no?
[PARN]
But... But the demon dragon
is attacking
the people of Flaim!
Exactly. And that makes it
a problem for Flaim alone.
You have your own
path to follow.
[PARN]
My own...
Do as your father did,
and gather together
the Holy Knights of Valis.
But... Highness!
And besides, you would only be
getting in the way
of my soldiers.
[gasps]
Your recklessness
during training
proved that you're not
yet ready for battle.
How long are you
going to pout?
[DEEDLIT]
Parn...
You should be glad you're not
going with him.
Don't you realize Shooting Star
is one of the ancient
dragons of Lodoss?
He's a lot stronger
than the one we fought.
An entire army of
soldiers couldn't defeat
a dragon like him.
[water trickling,
birds chirping]
Don't be upset. King Kashue is
just worried about you, Parn.
I know it. I know it!
[DEEDLIT giggles]
We haven't seen
the others for a long time.
Parn, I know you're
worried about Wood.
Whether he's fallen
under Karla's control?
Go away!
Parn, you know
it wasn't our fault,
even if Karla did get him.
[footsteps]
[VOICE] He who holds the Scepter
of Domination rules Lodoss...
Hah! Who are you?
What...? Impossible!
I see.
It would seem that you require
a human body to carry on
with your eternal life.
It is apparent that
any trash will do.
My name is Karla, and I
exist within no body.
[WAGNARD laughs]
Don't think
I will always be
moved by the
likes of you, Karla!
No, not Kardis!
[WAGNARD laughs]
Even a 500-year-old witch is no
match for Kardis the Destroyer!
After I unleash
the wrath of Kardis,
then the powers
of the gods are mine!
[KARLA] Tread carefully this
path you choose, Wagnard.
[chuckles]
Too late, Karla.
The gears have
already begun to turn!
[laughs]
[ASHRAM] He who holds
the sword rules Marmo.
He who holds the
Scepter of Domination
rules Lodoss...
You'll never make a good spy if
you can't hide your presence.
I shall be leaving you
for a short while, my lord.
So what has Wagnard
put you up to?
[gasps]
[grunts]
I shall be at your side again
before this wound heals clean.
[VILLAGERS chattering]
Capital of Valis, huh?
Pretty gloomy, ain't it?
The people have
just lost their king.
They'll need
some time to recover.
[SHIRIS] Tell me something
I don't know.
Are you
looking for someone?
Huh?
No one.
[SHIRIS gasps]
Your Highness,
what did you say to Parn?
[KASHUE] I told him
to follow his own path.
[ETOH]
But Parn is--
[KASHUE]
This is a dragon quest.
[ETOH]
King Kashue!
Etoh, you look after Fianna.
Hyah!
Kashue's headed here, too?
[MAN A] It would seem the
illustrious mercenary king
requires the scepter as well.
Let us dispose of
this pebble. Just say so.
--[horse whinnies]
--[ASHRAM] Whoa!
[grunting]
[gasping]
[yelling]
Hyah!
[ringing]
[roars]
Don't be so reckless, my lord!
You can't just throw your life
away like that. Our quest!
Demon sword, do you sense
your master has changed?
Demon sword of darkness.
[ETOH]
Parn, the tea's ready.
Well, King Kashue's
left us behind,
and we don't know where to start
searching for Woodchuck.
Not like us, eh, Parn?
Not knowing what's to be done?
Not even knowing
what we're here for.
Etoh.
[birds chirping]
[giggles]
[DEEDLIT gasps]
Hmph.
Deed!
[yells]
[PIROTESS] I wondered
what sort of challenge
a High Elf would present.
So what do you want, peasant?
Your reputation
as a stuck-up princess
seems quite well-deserved.
We should report
to Wagnard immediately.
No, we'll meet up
at Fire Dragon Mountain.
[DARK ELF A] But what
about the consequences?
[PIROTESS] Only he is
worthy of our loyalty.
[PARN panting]
Huh? Hey! It's you!
[SHIRIS]
I came to pay you back.
[PARN]
What?
Oh, come on! I'll help you.
[gasps]
It's her!
Stop it.
If we're gonna do this,
it's gonna be my way.
Understand?
The Dark Elves have
got your friend with them.
Two men and one woman.
She is the strongest.
All right. Now, you just
go out there and save
that friend of yours
and we can handle the rest.
[gasps]
[PIROTESS] "I summon the powers
of darkness to do my bidding.
Come to me. Drain the
power from my captive
so that I may fulfill
my sacred mission.
Sleep my prisoner, sleep."
[DARK ELVES gasp]
[SHIRIS yells]
No! Stop her!
[groans]
[PARN] What do you
want with her?!
[PIROTESS]
Huh?
--Hyuri!
--Oh!
[SHIRIS]
That's right!
Even you guys are
scared of berserkers!
And he won't hold back
because you're a lady!
I think that a retreat
would appear to be
in order right
about now. Hyah!
Deed! Deed!
Puh... Parn...
I'm all right...
Their spell... doesn't...
last very long...
They're...
Fire Dragon Mountain...
What is it?
The Marmo... to Fire Dragon...
Why are the Marmo headed there?
King Kashue's there!
[SHOOTING STAR roars]
[ASHRAM] Demon dragon,
wait for me.
Once I've beaten you
and recovered
the Scepter of Domination,
I will make
all of Lodoss mine.
[KASHUE]
Shooting Star...
This time, your sleep
will last all eternity.
The Marmo and Shooting Star?!
It won't be easy!
I don't care! I'm going
to help Kashue!
Didn't you clear
your debt to me already?
You guys look like
you're headed for some fun!
Right, Orson?
Thanks for your help back there.
I didn't expect to
hear that from an elf!
Don't worry! From here on,
we're with you!
Hey, that's good to know!
Now that Parn
has a path to follow,
there's no stopping him.
[NARRATOR]
Times change. People change.
There are those with ambitions,
and those who fight
to build a future.
And now, opposing
desires once again
move across Lodoss
to clash in a new struggle.
[SHOOTING STAR roars]
Let all the wonders
come to me
The fantasy fills,
fills my heart
I'll never wander anymore
For all the love I have,
I have for you
All the spirits of the wind
Spread their magic
wings and fly
Racing at the speed of light
Through the valleys
and the passages of time
When we fell in love
Destiny
Now each night
will have no end
Our nights will never end
Eternity awaits
You and me
Now that you are here
We'll never be alone again
Stay with me, my love