Aah, Blade... Seems like
ages since we've been here.
Yes, but it's only been
three years. Right?
Things sure have
changed a lot...
It's certainly more crowded.
No doubt due to the
influx of refugees
who are trying to escape
the chaos of the war.
It seems that everyone
craves peace.
But the only place
to find it in Lodoss
is here in Flaim or in
the free city of Raiden.
Hey, what's that?
[MAN A]
Why, you!
Is it a fight?
It looks that way.
Let's check it out!
But, Parn! We have to get to
King Kashue as soon as we--
Oh, why does this
always happen with him?
[CROWD gasps]
--Are you all right?
--Daddy!
[ALL gasp]
We've had enough!
Filthy refugees!
You should be grateful
King Kashue let you
stay here in Flaim.
But you all act like thieves!
You people are scum!
[ALL gasp]
[MAN A]
Look carefully, people!
Under King Kashue's rule,
Flaim considers theft
to be a serious crime!
What the--?!
Hyah!
Who do you think you are?!
I should be asking you that!
You are the one who's
attacking an unarmed man!
[DEEDLIT]
Are you all right?
But the man's a thief!
Look, he stole this!
Then shouldn't you
return it to its owner?
King Kashue would never
permit what you're doing!
Shut up! It's none of your
business, so stay out of it!
Don't you be foolish now.
You're gonna get hurt.
Parn!
I know! I'll go easy.
[MEN yelling]
Now, who's gonna be next?
Hold it! Hold it!
Just who are you people
and what do you
think you're doing
helping out these lowlives?
Now wait a minute!
Just hear me out.
Silence! You'd better
come along now,
and don't give me any trouble
or I'll cut you down.
If you're looking for
a fight, you found one.
Parn, no! You mustn't
fight with these men!
What?! P-Parn?!
Can it be? Wait!
Sheathe your swords,
all of you! Do it now!
A-Are you Parn, th-the knight
who saved Flaim from peril?
Well, I am Parn.
But to say that I saved
Flaim is an exaggeration.
Forgive us, sir!
We had no idea you
were coming to Flaim.
No, please. Forgive me for
interfering in this dispute.
But when I saw these militiamen
ganging up on that
unarmed refugee,
I just had to put a stop to it.
So that was your reason...
I understand.
But you must know there
is a serious food shortage
here in Flaim because
we've had so many refugees.
Are the people going hungry?
Yes, indeed.
And our citizens have grown
resentful of the refugees.
Disturbances like this
are a daily occurrence.
Now, Sir Parn, are
you headed for Akroyd?
Well, yes. Indeed, I am.
Then please allow me
to escort you to there.
Wow... I believed him when he
said he knew King Kashue,
but I didn't think
he was this famous.
But then again,
you knew I would never fall
for just some ordinary
fighter, right?
[GUARD A]
Open the gates! Open the gates!
[GUARD B]
That's Sir Parn!
[GUARD A] I'll announce
your arrival immediately.
Please wait here.
All right. And thank you
for the escort.
--[clanging]
--[KIDS grunting]
[PARN]
Huh?
It looks like they're the
future knights of Flaim.
Well, it looks like they've got
quite a ways to go
in their training.
[KID A]
Give up?
[SPARK]
No way!
I win again, Spark! Hah!
Oh, no. Not yet, you!
That kid is in good shape.
And he's got a clear
look... in his eyes.
I'd say he looks like
a young Parn.
You think so?
There's no need to be so formal.
To me, you will always
be my very good friends.
Please forgive us for not
staying in touch, King Kashue.
So he's Kashue...
The famous mercenary king...
You're looking well.
[PARN]
As are you, Your Highness.
[KASHUE]
I see three new faces.
A couple of mercenaries
and another sorcerer.
Looks like you're gearing up
for some trouble.
Yes, we are.
And we've come to ask a favor
of you, Your Highness.
[KASHUE] Now I understand
your purpose here.
Still, I cannot believe that
this is a mere coincidence.
[PARN]
What do you mean, Your Highness?
He means that our
goals are the same.
The army of Flaim is about
to embark on a mission
to find and kill Shooting Star.
It looks like everyone's going
to Fire Dragon Mountain.
Yes. He must be stopped.
Shooting Star has been on
a ravenous hunt for prey.
And his hunting ground
is western Flaim.
[KASHUE] The grassy plains
of our western region
have always provided Shooting
Star with ample prey.
Until recently, the land
was mostly unsettled,
and few dared to even
enter the region.
However, the recent
flood of refugees
has caused a severe
food shortage
and overcrowding here in Blade.
In an efford to solve
our domestic problems,
I had no alternative but
to establish a settlement
in the west.
[KASHUE]
The village burned to the ground
when Shooting Star attacked.
Not a single person
was left alive.
They all... died?
The fault lies in my
own naïve thinking.
But in order to feed
the people of Flaim,
we must be able
to use that land!
Definitely.
For a desert region like Flaim,
farmable land is vital.
[KASHUE] And as king,
I cannot forgive that dragon
for destroying our village.
That is why we are
preparing ourselves
to set out and kill
Shooting Star!
[PARN] In that case,
you can count on all of us
to lend our assistance. Right?
But Parn, Abram is still
on Blue Dragon Island.
So what?
[SLAYN]
There are two dragons.
There's Shooting Star and Abram.
And we have no way of knowing
which one holds the
Scepter of Domination.
If Abram is the one who
really has the scepter,
then while we're all off
killing Shooting Star...
...Ashram is off killing Abram.
And he would be the one
to get the scepter.
Then... what should we do?
It's simple. All we have
to do is send forces
to go after both of the
dragons simultaneously.
Splitting my forces would
be the right move.
But we haven't sufficient
numbers to do so.
And there'd be no one
left to defend Flaim.
Uh... But you won't
have to do that.
Ashram isn't running around
with a big army, is he?
So we should send a small force.
Just a few good men.
It's quality,
not quantity, am I right?
Quality, not quantity...
You tend to oversimplify.
But you make a good point.
If that's the case,
then you can leave the job
of killing Abram to us.
But you don't--
To kill Shooting Star,
the most experienced military
people should be used.
That's why we should be
the ones to go after Abram.
Parn, take Deed
and use your talents
where they're most needed.
You won't need the help of
a sorcerer's magic for this.
Highness, I believe Orson
should be the one
to lead us to Blue
Dragon Island.
O-Orson?
What happened here?!
[ASHRAM]
It seems the rumors
of Shooting Star's
restlessness are true.
They're all dead.
So this is the awesome power
of our enemy. Very well.
What's the matter?
Are you nervous, Priest Hobb?
I am a man of complete faith.
Myrii will protect us all.
That's just what I want to hear.
I have great hopes
for you, Priest. Hyah!
Hyah!
[SHIRIS] You want to
make Orson the leader?!
Yes. I've been thinking about
it since our journey began.
About how to help free Orson
from the spirit of anger.
And how to prevent him
from becoming a berserker.
The answer was in front
of me the whole time.
It was you, Parn. It was you!
Me?
Throughout our travels,
you have experienced so
many different things.
As our leader, more than
any of the rest of us,
you've learned to accept
the strong feelings
you carry inside you.
I see! If Orson is able
to learn to accept
the strong feelings
inside of him,
then he'll be released
from the spirit of anger!
Besides that,
he's quite level-headed.
Making decisions as a leader
should not be hard for him.
Do you really think
I'm level-headed?
Please wait. You know I don't
have what it takes to lead.
Besides, if I become
a berserker again,
there's no telling
who I might hurt.
Orson...
I believe in the strength
of your will, Orson.
Huh?
If you think like a leader
and act like one,
the result will be that you'll
feel like one in your heart.
Then, I'm certain that
the normal feelings
will reawaken within you.
Great idea! Let's try it out!
If it works, you won't
become a berserker again.
[gasps]
You're so distracted.
Is there something wrong?
Hm? No. I'm all right.
[SHIRIS]
Parn!
[PARN]
Huh?
Shiris...
[SHIRIS]
So, what do you think?
I hardly ever get
to wear a dress.
Uh... You look just fine.
[SHIRIS]
Thank you.
So would you like to dance?
No, thanks. I'm an awful dancer.
Who cares how bad you are?
But Parn!
[SHIRIS]
C'mon! C'mon!
[ORSON]
Thanks.
I thought Parn
was your boyfriend.
Doesn't this bother you?
I wonder sometimes.
After all, I'm an elf and
he's a human, you know?
Shiris really seems
to like Parn though.
How 'bout you? Do you mind?
I don't know.
I have no feelings.
I haven't felt love
since I was a child.
I see. But don't worry, though.
I'm sure this journey will
help you to feel once again.
I hope you're right.
If not, then making me
leader will be a waste.
[SHIRIS giggles] Come on,
Parn. Like this!
[PARN]
Uh, right.
[SHIRIS]
That's it-- Oh!
Ugh, why don't you watch--!
[SHIRIS gasps]
[SHIRIS] K-King Kashue!
Forgive me, Your Highness!
It's all right. You're the
new one. Shiris, isn't it?
Oh, yes. That's right.
Thank you, sire.
So Parn, are you
enjoing yourself?
Well-- Well, I--
Still honest as ever.
You must think it's wrong for us
to be having a party
to boost our morale
while others in Flaim are
going hungry, am I right?
[PARN]
No, i-it's not that...
But sharing in the
people's suffering
is not the job of the king.
My only job is to
save them from it.
I agree.
But as long as Shooting
Star lives, there's no way
to save the refugees
or the citizens of Flaim.
And there's another
threat--Ashram.
Uh... Your Highness?
Hmm? Oh, yes! I almost forgot.
Let me introduce you.
Hello.
I saw you this afternoon.
This is Spark. He shows
a lot of promise.
In exchange for serving me,
I'm letting him study
and train with us.
An honor, sir. It's really
a privilege to meet you.
It-- Well, it's my dream to
become a knight like you.
Why, thank you.
Oh, yes. You know, Parn,
every single young person
in Flaim looks up to you.
You are their model knight.
[PARN]
I'm their model?
Thank you, Spark.
I'm sure that one day,
you'll become an even
better knight than I am.
Now, Parn, let's dan--
[KASHUE]
Parn.
Maybe we can teach
young Spark a thing or two
if we spar for a little while.
You're reading my mind!
Oh! It's not fair!
Especially since I was
the one who stole him!
I know, you don't have
any feelings, Orson,
but could you at least
tell me that I look nice?
You look nice.
Gee, thanks a lot.
[DEEDLIT groans]
[clanging]
This is great!
[PARN]
Here he comes!
So, you parried it!
[PARN]
He's fantastic!
But what else could
I expect from him?
What do I do? What do I do?
Are you finished already?
[BOTH yell]
[PARN]
Y-You got me.
[KASHUE]
That was a very good charge.
But I see you still
get distracted.
Just charge in
and don't hold up.
If you hadn't stopped to think
about the consequences,
then you might have won.
Y-Yes, sir.
Thank you.
[KASHUE]
Tell me, Parn.
How would you like to be a king?
Uh... A king?
[KASHUE] I know what's
going on in Alania.
The villages in the north
have declared independence,
and a certain hero has
been causing trouble
for Duke Raster, hasn't he?
I'm not a hero. I haven't
been doing it alone.
So much of our success
is due to Slayn
and the rest of the
people of Zaxon.
But people seek out heroes,
especially in a world
so torn by war.
I would be glad see
you become king
and ascend the throne of Alania.
I think the people of Alania
would like that, too.
But I don't believe
I could ever have
what it takes to be a real king.
Oh, please. A king is just
a face for his kingdom.
Besides, you have
excellent friends.
If you need advice,
you can just ask for it.
[PARN]
Yes, but...
You must have heard the reports
about Valis's new king.
[PARN]
We've heard about it in Alania,
but we don't know
who the new king is.
Don't be too shocked now,
but the new king of Valis is
a very good friend of yours.
It's the High Priest, Etoh.
[gasps] You mean--
It's my Etoh?! Huh?!
Yes, and if he can do it,
then so can you.
Besides, all men
dream of being king.
This is a great chance for you.
I need some time to think.
[KASHUE]
Of course.
Save your decision until
this trouble is behind us.
But know that if you
do decide to be king,
Flaim will stand by
you all the way.
And besides that, Parn,
when you finally become king,
I will be able to treat
you as an equal.
And nothing would
make me happier.
[yells]
[PARN]
I have to concentrate now!
The dragon must die.
And we must crush Ashram's
ambitions for Marmo!
To ensure a safe
future for Lodoss!
--Welcome...
--...to Lodoss Island!
What you've all
been waiting for...
...the second part!
[giggles]
What's keeping King Kashue?
Tell me, is it true that he's
a master swordsman?
Oh, he sure gave Parn a
licking a few years ago.
[PARN]
Ouch.
[KASHUE]
All right, let's go!
There it is!
[BOTH stammering]
What's a knight in bed?
A "good knight!"
[groaning]
A wobbly shield?
A "shindo!"
A dragon sport?
Uh-- Um-- Uh--
A drampoline?
Don't answer a pun
with a question!
[KASHUE chuckles]
What kinda specialty is that?
I've got it! I've got it!
But what is it, Parn?
The king's opening line will be:
"I'm King Kashue,
and this is my cashew.
I'm really quite a nut!"
That's gotta be it!
[DEEDLIT, SHIRIS groan]
[giggles] Oh, Parn, come on!
Oh, please! That guy's the king!
He'd never come out using
a stupid line like that!
I... I guess not...
[KASHUE] You've grown
in your skills, Parn.
Oh, I'm so proud...
[sobbing]
[ALL]
We'll be seeing you!
[DEEDLIT]
The free city of Raiden.
The port leading to
Blue Dragon Island,
home of Abram, the water dragon.
But with the people of the
city living in fear of pirates,
no one dares to
venture out to sea.
What will our new
leader Orson decide?
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War:
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"Pirates... The Ship
of Dark Ambitions."