[growling]
[ORSON whimpers]
[ORSON'S SISTER]
Orson, forgive me.
[ORSON'S SISTER screams]
Stop it! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Leave me alone! Leave me alone!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! No!
[ORSON screams]
[LEYLIA]
"Marfa, mother of the Earth...
Use your power to heal him,
and return his body and his
spirit to what they were."
[NEESE coos]
Oh, Slayn... Is he
doing any better?
He'll live, but he's been
through a terrible strain.
His body and his spirit
are complete worn out.
I see...
That poor man.
His soul has been possessed
by Hyuri, the spirit of anger.
It's amazing he's been
able to last this long.
Orson is suffering through
a terrible ordeal.
I only wish I had the power
to completely rid him
of this possession.
I would prefer not to have
anything to do with a berserker.
No matter how
skilled the shaman,
no one has ever been able to
drive away the spirit of Hyuri.
[CECIL]
I agree!
What are we supposed to do
if he goes berserk again?
[PARN]
I'd rather not make an enemy
of someone I can't
beat with a sword.
And as for the enemies
I can beat, I, um--
I make exceptions for dragons.
I think it's about
time you told us.
What was it that
Neese said to you
at the temple of Marfa, Slayn?
All right, Parn.
You're entitled to understand.
And it's important for all
of you to understand
the mission we are
about to embark upon.
[LEYLIA]
We must begin our understanding
with the story of
the destruction
of the ancient kingdom
of Sorcery here in Lodoss.
Yes. It was 500 years ago...
The sorcerers of Lodoss had
brought honor and glory
to the ancient
kingdom of Kastuul.
Using their powerful sorcery,
they mastered the spirit world,
even making servants
of the dragons.
However, in their
quest to master
ever more powerful
forms of magic,
a group of them attempted
a grand magical experiment,
but failed miserably.
Their magic was sealed away,
and their holy land
was destroyed.
Now with their land in ruin,
and their powers gone,
the people of Kastuul were easy
prey for the barbarian tribes.
It was a bloody uprising.
[KARLA] How goes the battle,
Governor Saluvan?
Terribly. You and I are
the only nobles left alive.
The city is lost, Karla.
[KARLA]
So Kastuul has finally fallen
from its position of glory.
The last defenders
of the city of Kuudo
are the dragon's tooth warriors.
All we ever did was
abuse the barbarians.
If only we had just manipulated
them as Marfa taught.
I can't believe you're
a follower of Marfa.
It's because of
heretics like you
that we've actually
lost this war.
Not true.
We were destroyed because
we relied so much on our magic
that we forgot our
limits as humans.
You cannot fight destiny.
When we die,
this city will most certainly
sink beneath the lake.
At least we'll take
the barbarians with us.
Still, it's ironic, isn't it?
So long ago, the gods were
destroyed by the dragons,
and we of the
kingdom of Sorcery,
who had the power to tame them,
have been destroyed
by petty barbarians.
And why don't I see any of our
precious dragons around here?
Perhaps if we had used them,
we might have postponed
our deaths a bit more.
They are flying to secret
hideaways throughout Lodoss,
charged with the
duty of protecting
the most precious
treasures of Kastuul.
Someday, the power of our
kingdom will surely be revived.
That day will come.
And we must make sure
the magic of the Governor's
Treasures is not lost.
How useless.
In that case, I know now that
I must live on as I see fit.
This terrible destruction
must never be allowed
to happen again.
[SALUVAN]
So you'll commit your soul
to that circlet on your head?
Some immortality.
I pray that it's not your final
act as a sorceress, dear Karla.
For your sake,
I hope your plan works.
[SALUVAN chuckles]
[LEYLIA] After that,
Karla left to join the battle...
...and lost her life.
[LEYLIA] Then, through her
magical circlet,
she took the soul of the
barbarian who had killed her,
leaving the doomed city
of Kuudo behind her.
And that is all I know
about the ancient kingdom,
the only memory that Karla
has left inside of me.
[SLAYN] Now the most
important part of this story
is what Governor Saluvan did,
entrusting the five
ancient dragons
with what were known as
the Governor's Treasures,
and having them hidden in
places throughout Lodoss.
I've heard that story before!
A lot of adventurous people have
tried to find that treasure.
And somehow, they
all wind up dead.
But suppose that a man appeared
who is able to kill the dragons,
and suppose he claimed
the Governor's Treasures
for himself, what
would you think then?
If he was a man
with a just heart,
it would not be a problem.
But if he was evil,
it could be a disaster.
[gasps] Hold on!
Are you telling us that such
a man has actually appeared?!
The ice dragon Bramd has
just been killed in his lair.
He was murdered at the hand
of the famous black knight
who seeks the treasure of
the Scepter of Domination.
And with it, the power to
control every living thing!
[gasps]
He's returned again, Parn.
It's Ashram.
Ashram...
[PARN]
I'll never forget him.
Back during the War of Heroes,
Ashram was the captain
of the royal guard
for Emperor Beld of Marmo.
Marmo?!
Oh, no way!
If a man like that
gets his hands
on the Scepter of Domination,
it would be a disaster!
[SLAYN] That's why we have to
get the Scepter of Domination
before Ashram does.
Even if it means we
have to fight a dragon.
[CECIL]
But wouldn't it be a lot easier
if we just kill this
Ashram guy instead?
I wish I could say yes.
But we're talking about a man
who made it to White
Dragon Mountain
and was able to
single-handedly kill Bramd.
And I'm afraid it's
almost a certainty
that he was able to kill the
evil dragon Narse on Marmo.
So you must make a choice as
to the more formidable foe:
Is it the dragon or
the dragon slayer?
Neither one is a
very good choice.
But this must be done.
If we were forced to
endure another war
like the War of Heroes,
then all of Lodoss would
surely turn to ashes.
By the way, Slayn,
do you have any idea
which dragon holds the
Scepter of Domination?
Well, since the dragon
riders of Moss
have no real
control over Lodoss,
I think it is safe to assume
that the king dragon Mycen
is not the one who
holds the scepter.
[PARN]
That leaves only two others.
[SLAYN] Yes. There's Shooting
Star of Fire Dragon Mountain,
and Abram,
of Blue Dragon Island.
One of them holds the scepter.
Can we rely on your help?
Brave Parn?
Of course, my friend.
We cannot allow ourselves
to fail in this endeavor.
We must devise a
most careful plan.
[PARN]
I have an idea, Slayn.
I think we should
travel to Flaim.
We should ask King Kashue
for his assistance on this.
Believe it or not,
I was just thinking
the same thing, myself.
The kingdom of Flaim
is directly on our path
to Fire Dragon Mountain,
as well as Blue Dragon Island.
Besides, I'm sure he'll help us.
Tomorrow, we will
set out for Flaim.
Prepare yourselves.
Destiny commands...
...and we must obey!
[NARRATOR]
At first light,
Parn and his party made final
preparations for their journey.
And with the sun
climbing into the sky,
they set out on the path to the
three desert kingdoms of Flaim,
leaving Zaxon village
far behind them.
Hyah!
Uh?! Whoa!
[PARN]
Shiris! Orson!
[SHIRIS]
It's not polite to leave
without saying
goodbye, Parn.
I still haven't paid you
back for saving my life.
Well, I-- I, um-- Ah...
I really appreciate
the thought, but please,
this just isn't the time.
Says who? I can repay a debt.
And that's the reason why
I've decided to come along
and help all of you in your
quest to kill that dragon!
[PARN]
Huh?
You're gonna what?!
[SHIRIS] Despite appearances,
I'm a pretty darn good fighter,
and I can be of use to you,
so let me come, Parn!
B-But--
I'm against it! Imagine!
Taking some girl who just rode
in from God knows where...
And besides, she's a
mercenary for Duke Raster!
That deal is history!
I'm on my own!
But I wonder if it's such
a good idea for the captain
of the self-defense force to
just up and leave the village.
The village will be protected
by the holy soldiers of Marfa
and the dwarf clan to the north!
Mind your own business!
And I'm still
against her coming!
Unfortunately, nobody asked you!
So shut up, you greenhorn!
What did you call me?!
[PARN] Enough! Both of you,
cut it out right now!
If you're going to pick fights,
you don't have to come!
Which means I can come as
long as I don't pick a fight.
Well, I guess...
Her actions since yesterday
have led me to place
trust in her word.
And... we need all the help
that we could possibly get.
[CECIL]
Master Slayn!
And you?
I think she--
Um, whatever you
think is best, Parn.
[PARN]
All right, you can come.
But don't do anything rash.
This is really dangerous.
I knew you'd agree!
And don't worry!
Facing a strong enemy just
encourages me to fight harder!
[PARN chuckles]
[gasps]
[growls]
I want to say thank you.
For healing me.
Sure.
Just a minute!
Who said the berserker
could come along?
Orson and I are partners!
We've been working
together for many years.
Do I look worried to you?
But Slayn...
Deedlit...
Suppose I told you that he
was my very good friend,
would you agree to let
him come along then?
[gasps]
[PARN] Do you remember
Leylia's story from last night?
[SHIRIS]
Mm-hm.
Well, she left out one
very important detail.
[SHIRIS]
What is it?
She didn't mention the fact
that Karla, the Grey Witch,
is still alive.
And she's taken one
of my old friends.
Woodchuck was a bad thief,
but a good friend.
Karla's power and personality
are sealed in
that golden circlet.
Whoever wears it becomes
possessed by her.
Drifting from body to body
throughout the centuries,
she's been able to achieve
her coveted immortality.
And so, she continues
to be responsible
for all the war and all
the chaos in Lodoss.
But why? Why does she cause it?
The kingdom of Sorcery
destroyed itself.
All because of its pursuit
of absolute power.
Karla believes that by
shifting the power base
between the kingdoms,
she can ensure eternal
prosperity for Lodoss.
But that means that the War
of Heroes five years ago...
[PARN] Right. Karla
controlled the whole thing.
And the body that held
the circlet back then was...
Oh, no! You mean--?
[PARN] Leylia is desperate to
atone for the chaos she caused
while her body was
under Karla's control.
Even to the point of enduring
a dangerous journey
to help avoid a war.
Or like saving a warrior
whose heart is controlled
by the spirit of anger.
Boy, you've got a big
mouth, Mr. Free Knight.
Besides, look.
[CECIL sighs]
Come, we must hurry onward.
It's vital that we cross
the mountains
and get ourselves to Flaim
as quickly as we can.
You're so right.
[PARN]
To protect the land of Lodoss,
I have to get to King
Kashue as fast as I can!
[NARRATOR] At that moment,
just outside of Blade,
the capital of the desert
kingdom of Flaim,
Hobb, priest of
the War God Myrii,
is visited at the temple
by a company of strangers
clad in thick, black armor.
I'll ask you one more time!
You honestly expect
that I would abandon the post
given me by King Kashue
to help you and your
knights of Marmo?
For a priest of the war god,
is there no greater honor
than to teach brave knights
to be more powerful?
Help me. I need the
power you possess.
I can't believe
that you would dare
to put yourself on a level
with King Kashue.
It's exactly where I belong.
[HOBB]
Ridiculous!
King Kashue is a true hero!
It was he who helped
kill Emperor Beld
in the War of Heroes!
And so, he thinks only
of his own kingdom,
not caring about the condition
of those around it.
Is that your definition
of a "true hero"?
[gasps]
Marmo was destroyed in a war.
No one will deny that.
But Emperor Beld had a
dream of uniting Lodoss,
and that dream
still lives within me.
Kashue's contentment
with only ruling Flaim
is proof that he is nowhere
near the man Beld was!
[gasps]
So who really deserves
the title of "true hero"?
The priests of Myrii
call themselves
the "Seekers of Heroes," right?
You should know the answer.
[HOBB]
But Beld is dead now.
And there's no way
anyone can prove that!
That's a simple matter.
Kashue is mine. I'll conquer
Flaim and become king!
I will carry on for Beld.
His dream lives!
For I hold in my
hand the instrument
that will make me
worthy of such glory!
You will see this for
yourself in the near future.
[laughing]
[NARRATOR]
Four days later,
Parn and his party
arrived in Flaim.
And the priest Hobb
vanished from his post
at the temple of Myrii.
--Welcome...
--...to Lodoss Island!
What you've all been
waiting for...
...the second part!
[giggles]
Hi there! You can
call me Deedlit!
I love nature! I'm friends
with all the spirits.
I'm a high elf!
[giggles]
And... I'm the cutest
girl in the world.
Piling it on a little thick,
eh, little Deed?
Of course, my long ears
are very lovely,
along with my waist, my bust,
and of course, my shapely hips.
And my age is a secret!
Big deal.
Just 'cause she's a high elf,
she acts like she's a
princess or something!
Oh, Deed...
I don't know what he sees
in that older woman.
Having an older girlfriend
is really quite
fashionable nowadays.
Older?!
You mean you didn't know?
Even though elves
look really young...
...they actually age much
faster, so she's really--
[screams]
[PARN]
160 years old?!
That is why I said...
...my age is a secret!
Anyway, using my very own
shamanistic magic,
I will help to defend
the one I love!
Yay!
[DEEDLIT]
And now...
[PARN cheers]
And now, folks!
Presto! Just kidding!
[DEEDLIT laughing]
Love that shamanistic magic!
[GROUP groans]
Yes! I will keep trying!
[PARN grunting]
[SLAYN]
Are you really sure we should be
traveling with this guy?
Never bring that up either!
[ALL]
We'll be seeing you!
[PARN] Now reunited with our
old comrade, King Kashue,
we decide to take on Shooting
Star, the fire dragon, together!
At a glittering party
before our adventure,
the king presents an
unexpected proposal.
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War :
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"King...The Long Sought Hero."