[NARRATOR]
Light and darkness...
The final battle of the gods
climaxed in a clash between
Marfa, goddess of all creation,
and Kardis, goddess
of destruction.
At the end of their
fierce battle,
the stricken goddesses
had split the continent,
forming a new land.
Since then, people have come
to call this new continent
"Lodoss - The Accursed Island."
The way that you
embrace me with your
strong and powerful arms
Your haunting words keep me
close to everything about you
Romantic in ways
in ways that almost
tear upon my heart
Can't let you go
Don't you know?
Io sono prigioniera
A captive in
your gentle hands
A prisoner of
your soulful eyes,
your special smile
will never part
If the morning sun
should free me
It really wouldn't let me go
I'd still be caught
inside your love
Can't rise above
the chains of your heart
[thunder cracks]
[NARRATOR] Marmo, the island
soaked in the blood of Kardis,
goddess of madness
and destruction.
Deep beneath ground so
defiled it could not even
be purified by Marfa,
the Earth mother,
Kardis malevolently
awaits her rebirth.
The resurrection of Kardis
requires the sacrifice
of a High Elf's eternal life.
Knowing this, Wagnard,
the Marmo wizard,
has acquired immense power to
control the events to come.
With the Scepter of Domination
and Deedlit the High Elf
safely in hand,
Wagnard is now ready
to begin the
resurrection ceremony.
[WAGNARD] High Elf,
in exchange for your life,
Kardis will be reborn.
And when the world
is filled with death,
the one who possess
the scepter shall live.
And I, Wagnard, will
control Kardis herself.
[chuckles]
[roars]
[DEEDLIT]
Parn...
[KOBOLD A screams]
[NARRATOR] Should Kardis'
resurrection begin,
Deedlit's life would
hang by a thread.
Hoping to save her,
Parn and the others
have arrived
in Marmo ahead of
King Kashue's
main force.
[groaning]
[PARN panting]
[PARN] We've gotta
get past those monsters.
The altar of the Dark God,
Falaris, is up ahead.
She's there, Slayn?
Most probably.
Hold on, Deed.
It's been awhile since we've
fought together, sir.
This time, our adversary
could well be a god.
At least it's a
worthy foe, my lord.
Well, I suppose some degree
of bravado is appropriate,
but the resurrection of Kardis
must be stopped at any cost.
If not, then Lodoss is...
What is it, sire?!
[ship creaking]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Show no fear!
Let the arrows fly! Fire!
[yelling continues]
[MONSTER screeches]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
He's destroying the ship!
[yelling continues]
We will not die in the sea!
We will make it to Marmo!
[MONSTER screeches]
Huh?!
[JESTER]
I thought we were allies!
What're you doing going off
to fight by yourselves?
What about you two?
I thought you wanted
out of this job.
And let you guys
have all the fun? No way!
If the powers of
darkness grow stronger,
Hyuri might take control of me.
So, Orson, even a
berserker won't allow
Kardis to be reborn, eh?
Shiris would not
be protected by Hyuri.
[MARMO growling]
[yelling]
[yells]
--King Kashue...
--Look well, Shadam.
Even if we make it back alive,
we'll never return here.
Or, perhaps, there'll be
no place to return to.
To live as humans, you mean.
[PARN panting]
[yells]
[PARN]
Eeyah! Ah!
[KOBOLD B yells]
[panting]
--[GOBLIN A yells]
--[PARN gasps]
[groans]
There's no time to look back!
Think only of moving forward!
[thunder cracks]
[roars]
[WORT]
Hmm?!
So, Karla, what are these
"scales of history"?
What is this
"balance of power"?
No! It can't be!
Slayn, look.
What is that thing?
Kardis' blazing evil.
The ceremony is
probably down there.
Then let's go.
[ETOH gasps]
Parn!
[groans]
[KASHUE]
Huh?!
No! Parn's in there!
[ORSON]
Wait.
[roars]
What is that thing?
The ancient dragon of Marmo.
He's called Narse.
If Narse has already
shown himself, then...
[gasps]
"To my staff, I call
the power of light..."
[ETOH] To think that this exists
beneath Falaris' shrine...
[LEYLIA] As though Kardis was
asleep within Falaris' womb.
Kardis was the evil goddess
of madness and destruction,
loyal to the Dark God Falaris.
When Lodoss was separated
from the continent,
it is said that Kardis fell into
a deathly sleep beneath Marmo.
--[rumbling]
--[ALL gasp]
What's going on?!
Kardis is awakening. The
ceremony has already begun.
Deed!
Once the High Elf's eternal life
has been completely absorbed,
I will have fulfilled
all the requirements,
and the grand ancient
power will be reborn!
[laughs]
[WAGNARD] "Kardis, dark goddess
of madness and destruction!
Obey the ancient covenant!
Answer our summons to you!"
[WAGNARD] "Kardis! Dark goddess
of madness and destruction!
Obey the ancient covenant!
Answer our summons to you!"
[whimpers]
[whimpering continues]
Parn...
[footsteps]
--Huh?
--Parn, what's wrong?
Be careful, Parn.
Don't worry.
[BOTH gasp]
[PARN grunts]
[SLAYN] Don't use your sword!
It uses its fluid as a weapon!
[gasps]
[screams]
Hang on, Leylia!
Yah!
--[PARN] Leylia!
--[SLAYN] Stay back!
[SLAYN]
We can handle this!
Go on, Parn!
But, Slayn, you--
Wagnard cannot be allowed
to acquire Kardis' power!
You're the only one who can
stop him, Parn! You alone!
Now, go! Hurry now!
--I can't just--
--Parn! Let's go!
But they'll--!
--Are you ready?
--Yes.
"Omnipotent power,
creator of all things..."
"...throw off these
false garments
and reveal they true form.
Become a barrier
to protect us."
[NARSE roars]
[JESTER]
Keep away from the front!
You'll be caught in the flames!
[MERCENARY screams]
What's that thing
want with us?!
I'd say he doesn't want us
getting too close to him.
He's in our way.
[SHIRIS] Orson,
it's impossible! Orson!
--What is that?
--[KASHUE] Huh?
[JESTER]
Ah! Mycen!
[MYCEN growls]
[JESTER]
Right, we understand!
Kashue! The golden dragon
Mycen will deal with Narse!
Don't worry!
[KASHUE grunts]
[roars]
[WORT] Karla! Is Kardis'
resurrection necessay
to balance the scales
of history?!
[KARLA] For 500 years, my soul
has resided in this circlet
for the singular purpose
that I watch over Lodoss,
nothing more.
History must be
written by humans.
[WORT] And you aren't
human, is that it?
You think you're
the eyes of the gods
looking down
from the heavens?
Tell me if those eyes
will be watching silently
as Kardis is reborn.
[KARLA]
Did I not tell you?
I exist for only
one purpose:
to save Lodoss
from destruction.
[mumbles]
You give your life to empower
a magnificent goddess.
[chuckles]
[MAN groans]
But I thought you...
[ASHRAM] When did I ever allow
you to do whatever you wanted?
[WAGNARD] Who carried you
back from the netherworld?
I see, you've thrown your
lot in with that witch!
The powers of the gods are
beyond any man's abilities.
Even yours, Wagnard.
You should know your limits.
[chuckles]
Unfortunately, my limits
aren't quite the question here.
But Kardis' are!
[BOTH panting]
[BOTH gasp]
[PARN growls]
[PARN]
Hyah!
[groans]
[ETOH]
Parn!
[BOTH gasp]
[ETOH yells]
Etoh!
It's all right!
I'll handle this thing!
--You keep going!
--No way!
By the awesome powers of Falis!
My prayers will
do more than swords!
--Don't worry, just go!
--Etoh!
Go now! Hurry up, Parn!
Think about Deedlit!
You know what we came here for!
If you save Deed, you save
all of Lodoss as well!
I'm glad we made it this far
together, you and me.
Thanks, Etoh...
By the glory of Falis!
[WAGNARD] You wish to
continue living in shame?
[ASHRAM] Neither Marmo nor
Lodoss is your plaything.
[WAGNARD laughs]
Mere trifles, at best.
When the powers
of the gods are mine,
nothing else will matter.
What I desire is the power!
And when I have it,
I shall be invincible.
[grunts]
[DEEDLIT groans]
You're pathetic.
Now, know my wrath.
[ASHRAM grunts]
[DEEDLIT]
Parn... Forgive me...
I can't...
Let all the wonders
come to me
The fantasy fills,
fills my heart
I'll never wander anymore
For all the love I have,
I have for you
All the spirits of the wind
Spread their magic
wings and fly
Racing at the speed of light
Through the valleys
and the passages of time
When we fell in love
Destiny
Now each night
will have no end
Our nights will never end
Eternity awaits
You and me
Now that you are here
We'll never be alone again
Stay with me, my love