Kardis, the time is near!
The keys are here!
Soon now...
Soon you will be released
from your eternal prison.
Just wait, little Doorway...
[WAGNARD laughs]
[NARRATOR] After reuniting with
Parn and the Kanon free army,
Spark and the others
accompanied them
to the army's hidden fortress.
There, Neese reveals her
cursed fate to Parn.
Now he, too, understands
the true peril at hand.
[PARN]
I'm so sorry, Neese.
Such hardship.
No, this is my destiny.
We know that Wagnard
already has the two keys
he needs to initiate the
resurrection of Kardis--
the Soul Crystal Ball
and the Staff of Life--
but I'd sooner die than
to let him have Neese!
[gasps]
We're all counting on you.
Yes, sir!
[PARN] I welcome you again,
knight in training Spark.
Or do you finally have
the formal title of knight?
Well, it's actually
just the opposite.
I've had my qualifications
as a knight revoked.
I see...
Well, relax a little.
Right.
You all look like you've
had a rough time.
Please, come.
Oh, yes, ma'am!
"Oh, yes, ma'am..."
[LEAF]
What was that?!
Nothing.
Um, Sir Parn?
What is it?
If you wouldn't mind,
could you please update us
on the war situation?
We've been travelling on our own
for so long, we haven't
heard a thing.
I see. Not surprising.
Now then, you know about King
Kashue leading the army of Flaim
into the kingdom of
Alania, don't you?
[SPARK]
Yes, we know about that.
[PARN] Kashue's army defeated
the Alanian forces in
a terrible battle near Novice,
and now he's got them surrounded
in the capital city of Alan.
[NARRATOR] King Kashue,
trying to preserve Alan,
has repeatedly offered terms
of surrender to Duke Raster,
the self-appointed
leader of Alania.
However, Raster, has continually
refused to accept.
[RASTER wheezes, laughs]
[gasps] Kashue!
I warned you, didn't I?
I told you that if you
didn't want Alan to burn,
if you cared at all
about your citizens,
all you had to do...
...was surrender your
forces on my terms.
What the hell is
wrong with you?!
How many innocent people have
died because of your actions?!
The actions of a king!
A man who is supposed
to protect his subjects!
Unforgiveable!
[screams]
[swords clang]
[gasps]
[KASHUE snarls]
[RASTER screams]
[NARRATOR] And so, Alan fell.
And with it, the rest of Alania.
Uniting the conquered
forces with his own,
Kashue turned his
complete attention
toward defeating the Marmo.
Meanwhile, upon learning
of Alania's defeat,
King Etoh of the
holy kingdom of Valis
decided to launch a
full-state counterattack
against the Marmo as well.
With Etoh's leadership and
power as the High Priest,
those faithful to
the god of Light
became holy warriors
unafraid of death,
as the holy magic
was brought to bay.
King Etoh declared war?
Yes. He's committed to
this with all his heart.
And yet, the Marmo continue
to cause problems for us.
Damn them!
Just calm down, Spark! I've got
a plan and I need your help!
Yes! Anything you want!
[MARMO DRIVER yells]
[horse whinnies]
[MARMO A]
Enemy attack!
[yelling]
[GREEVUS yells]
[GARRACK]
You wanna fight, boys?
[SPARK growls]
[MARMO D growls]
[SPARK yells]
Ahh!
[MARMO groaning]
Stay alert, Spark!
Yes, sir!
[SPARK grunts]
[yells]
[horse whinnies]
What?! Whoa, looks like their
reinforcements have arrived.
Captain! Captain!
[SPARK]
Here I come!
What the...?
Greevus, get over here!
[GARRACK] There must be 30...
No, at least 40 of them!
What do we do, Spark?!
We fight! This is no time
to be running away!
Well said, Spark.
Now, let's go show
them our power.
Right.
Let's go!
[ALL yell]
[FREE ARMY LOOKOUT] They're
back! And they're all right!
[PARN]
Well done, Spark.
Thanks to you, our ambush
was a great success.
Don't thank me.
I know it doesn't seem like
much, but stealing supplies
like this really does the
enemy some damage over time.
Right.
[PARN] Anyway, now we're ready.
It's time for our forces
to head out and join
Prince Reona in Roodo.
The Marmo are almost finished.
So to give some meaning to all
this hard work you've done,
I thought you and your
friends might enjoy
a quiet victory banquet tonight.
I hope you'll be able
to stay for it.
Yes! We'd be honored, sir.
Well, later then.
Nice work, Parn.
Oh, Neese!
Look! They're all just fine!
And now I can relax...
You had doubts?!
Well, it doesn't look
like an easy time.
Even the Marmo aren't idiots.
After all those ambushes,
they're assigning more escorts.
Uh?!
You're hurt!
Uh... No, it's really
just a scratch, Neese.
This is hardly just
a scratch, Spark.
I'll heal it for you.
Now go and get it washed out
with water right away!
Please, Neese. I'm telling you,
I'm all right.
[NEESE]
Don't walk away from me!
[SPARK]
I said I'm fine!
[NEESE]
I'm still going to heal it.
I've got an idea, Neese. Why
don't you come and fix me up?
Good idea. And Spark,
I'll heal you instead.
Can't you be a little sensitive?
Huh?!
A seed shouldn't be disturbed.
I see no seed--
[RYNA]
Just leave them.
Uh... Lady Neese-- Huh?!
[LEAF]
You, too, Aldo.
[ALDO]
Hey, lemme go! Lady Neese!
Um...
Now let's go get
that wound washed out.
[NEESE]
How's that?
[SPARK]
It feels pretty good.
[NEESE]
I'm glad. Really, Spark.
How'd you do that?
[NEESE] Hmm? Oh...
Healing people is something
that comes naturally to me.
Anyway, I want to
help with banquet.
[SPARK]
Yes, I should get back, too.
[NEESE]
Let's go, then.
Right...
A banquet sure takes
a lot of work.
[LEAF]
Hey, Neese! How'd it go?
[NEESE]
How'd it go? What do you mean?
Come on, quit playin' dumb.
You got your chance to be
alone with Spark, didn't you?
Did you make your confession?
Your young maiden's confession?
Confession?
"Oh, my dear Spark,
I have always, always,
always loved you!"
"Oh, Neese. The truth is,
I've always loved you, too."
"Oh, Spark!"
"Oh, Neese!"
[BOTH sigh]
Leaf stop! Ryna, cut it out!
[GREEVUS]
Now Leaf, Ryna.
If you're not going to help us
to prepare for the banquet,
then please leave us alone.
[BOTH]
Sure...
Keep on peeling, Neese.
Right.
[GARRACK]
Hey, Captain Captain.
What now?
So, how did it go with the girl?
What? Huh? What girl?
Don't play dumb with me. You
know I'm talking about Neese.
Neese?!
I just heard it from Leaf.
Just what I'd expect
from my captain.
You've stolen the heart
of that little priestess.
[gasps]
The granddaughter of Neese,
one of the Six Heroes?
Man, what a score!
Garrack, I don't know what
you're talking about!
And at a time like this,
when you know that I've sworn
to protect her?!
[ALDO]
How dare you?!
[SPARK] Aldo! I didn't lay
a finger on her, honest!
Who said anything
about touching her?
I heard you two are in love
Now, look!
In love?!
[SPARK]
Listen to me!
So, what really happened between
you and Neese, Captain?
Leaf seems to think you two
had a nice time together
out in the woods.
What?
[SPARK grunts]
Just lay off!
[chatter, laughter]
[PARN chuckles]
Where are Ryna and Leaf?
I've got a bone
to pick with them.
They said they'd be along
any time now, Captain.
You should eat something.
This stuff is great! [belches]
No, thanks. I'm all right.
Oh, really?
Spark... When it's
time to eat, you eat.
You're right.
Now listen to the priest, Spark.
Tell me, Spark, how're
you enjoying yourself?
Ah. Fine.
Good. Today, we all eat,
drink, and make merry.
[LEAF] Captain!
Take a look at me, Spark!
[gasps]
Miss Deedlit! What a nice night!
Leaf, where have you been?
The banquet's already begun
and you're late!
Oh, Captain! You've got
to learn to lighten up.
Ryna and I were very busy
getting dressed up
for the banquet.
Dressed up? Oh really? You don't
look any different to me.
[growls]
When you're as
beautiful as I am,
you don't really have to
dress up to look adorable.
Now, look, Leaf--
No, you need to look
at this! Ta-dah!
[SPARK gulps]
[GARRACK]
Oh...
I guess... I look pretty funny.
[LEAF] Neese looks pretty,
right? Come on, Captain,
this is a new look for her.
Give her a compliment.
--[GARRACK] Wow...
--Lady Neese, you're lovely...
[LEAF] I wasn't talking to you
guys. I meant the captain!
Ah! Um... You, um... look nice!
Why, thank you, Captain.
Uh... Um... Uh.
Sure looks like love.
[PARN]
Mm...
Hey, Parn?
Uh...
We haven't danced in awhile.
Hey, uh, Dee!
[DEEDLIT] Refusing an invitation
from a lady, Sir Free Knight?
[PARN chuckles]
I guess I have no choice.
Heh. It would be my
pleasure... milady.
[music plays]
They're great...
Come on, Spark, don't just
watch. Ask Neese to dance.
[SPARK]
J-Just wait a minute, here!
It isn't proper to dance with--
Listen! When a girl
gets all dressed up,
it's a knight's duty
to dance with her!
Neese, you deserve
to have a little fun.
Yes.
Shall we?
Sure.
Oh, Lady Neese...
[SPARK] I don't know
what they want us to do.
I'm really sorry about
stepping on your foot
when we were dancing.
Oh... It's all right.
I had a wonderful time.
The most fun I've
ever had... I think...
...in my entire life.
[SPARK] In your entire life?
You can't be serious.
You see, Spark, ever
since I can remember,
my life has been
devoted to Marfa,
and I don't think the Earth
Goddess would approve
of her priestess having
fun with other people.
As a priestess, I must
be especially careful
to keep my heart pure.
And before, when we
were dancing, well...
I never felt that way before.
So, I imagine Marfa must
be very angry with me.
[SPARK]
I think you're wrong about that.
[gasps]
Having fun, being
happy and sad...
That's part of what it
means to be human, Neese.
Even a priestess can't cut
herself off from other people.
It wouldn't be fair.
Ah! I... I'm sorry, Neese.
How can I say that
when I know nothing about you?
[NEESE] If you wanna
know the truth, Spark,
King Etoh told me the same thing
just before we left Valis.
He said I didn't have to
work so hard just because
I'm a priestess.
That there's only so much
one person can do.
But I've grown to care
for all of you so much,
that sometimes I lose
my perspective.
I don't mean to push myself,
but I don't always know
how to react to my feelings.
To be honest with you, Spark,
I'm jealous of Leaf and Ryna.
They're so open with their
feelings all the time.
The way I am, everything
hurts too much.
[RYNA]
Come on.
[LEAF]
Hey, wait...!
[SPARK]
Neese...
[NEESE]
Oh, Spark, I...
Don't you worry about it, Neese.
When this journey is over, I'm
certain your pain will go away.
Let's both believe that.
Hmm.
[BOTH gasp]
[SPARK gasps]
[WAGNARD]
You insignificant flea!
How dare you corrupt
the Doorway's heart?!
The sacrifice to Kardis
must remain pure!
I'll not let you interfere!
It's Wagnard!
[gasps]
The time has come
for me to take you.
And now, we shall journey
to the dark island.
It is your destiny.
You cannot fight it.
[NEESE]
No! Let me go!
[SPARK growls, yells]
"Darkness of the blackest pitch,
I command you to
become a dark shield
and repel this aggressor."
[gasps] Spark!
Spark, run!
[SPARK growls]
[yells]
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Heh!
[SPARK grunts]
No! Spark!
And now, Doorway,
we shall return to the
dark island of Marmo!
[NEESE]
Spark! Spark! Spark...!
Neese!
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've
all been waiting for,
the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
[NEESE] The freakin' moon's
pretty, ain't it?
[SPARK]
Sure is.
[NEESE]
A shootin'-freakin'-star.
I think we're supposed
to make a wish.
[SPARK]
Mm!
What did you wish for, Neese?
Uh... It's a secret.
How 'bout you, Spark?
Mine's a secret, too.
[BOTH chuckle nervously]
[screaming]
[BOTH giggle]
[NEESE]
That must've freakin' hurt!
Oh, it was nothing, really.
I'm a knight in
training, remember?
Neese, what I wished
before was...
Yee-haw!
What would you do if the
Black Knight attacked you?
Beat him off!
[SWORDS]
Beat him off! Beat him off!
Spark, you've
gotten so clever...
I'm happy beyond all words...
[wails]
Excuse me.
[SPARK] I wonder what King
Kashue was doing here.
[NEESE]
You shoulda asked him!
What am I, a freakin'
mind reader?!
[SPARK]
All right, you're alone again.
Don't blow it this time.
[PARN]
I am not an old man!
[DEEDLIT] Parn! Wait up!
I'm sorry! Slow down, Pops!
[PARN]
I'm not old!
[SPARK whines]
Why does everything
keep getting in the way...?
[NEESE]
Come on, Spark.
Thank you, Neese.
Sure thing. I know some
special "magic" that'll help
heal that dragon bite
for ya, Spark.
Sure, Neese, whatever you say.
Let's get a room.
[SPARK]
Whoa, yeah!
[NEESE, SPARK]
We'll be seeing you...
[SPARK]
I wasn't able to protect Neese,
and now the Destroyer's
ressurection
is only a matter of time.
But Parn, the free knight,
calmly continues to make plans
for on our advance on Roodo.
What should I do? I have
to decide on the first step
towards saving Neese.
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War :
Chronicles of
the Heroic Knight :
"A Vow...
A Step Towards the Future."