[SOLDIERS shouting, chattering]
Defend the north
gate at all cost!
Evacuate the women
and children to Tarba!
Damn! If they hadn't
attacked so suddenly...!
This is no time for excuses!
We know what we have to do now.
--[crash]
--[CECIL] Huh?!
[SOLDIERS shouting, chattering]
Fall back, men!
We're retreating to Tarba!
But Cecil! We can still
fight these men.
The free army of Zaxon
will never live down
the disgrace of running away!
And I'll never be able to
face Slayn or Parn again
if I let you die!
Listen, it's true we may
have lost this battle...
...but in the end,
we will win the war!
I promise you that.
[CECIL] Damn you, Raster!
You and your Marmo allies.
[NARRATOR] The fires of
a new war have begun
to ignite on the island
of Lodoss once again.
Duke Raster, the Alanian
nobleman with a long history
of inciting unrest,
has formed an alliance
with the Marmo,
beginning a campaign to secure
all Alanian lands for himself.
[RASTER]
Those damned Zaxon peasants
have caused enough trouble!
But still... Why didn't I
think of doing this before?
It's so simple.
[UNDERLING A] Yes, but will
history forgive us for this?
[UNDERLING B] I agree.
Taking over Alania is one thing,
but some might say that
our alliance with the
dark island of Marmo
is sheer madness--
[growls]
Ah!
[RASTER]
Are you criticizing me?!
I, Raster?! The future
king of all Lodoss?!
You heard me.
First, I take over Alania.
Then, all of Lodoss
will be mine.
[laughing]
[GREEVUS]
So, this is the city of Hiruto.
Just what you'd expect
from a castle town.
[CROWD chattering]
[GARRACK]
Hey, this town is hopping.
It's not exactly what
you'd expect to find
in the middle of nowhere.
Well, this is the
second-largest city in Flaim.
Yeah, and maybe we'll
finally be able to find some
more information on those Dark
Elves we've been following.
[NEESE]
Mm... Hm...?
Uh. Lady Neese. What is it?
[SPARK]
Huh?
[NEESE]
It is the will of the gods.
I am following a dark nightmare.
[SPARK]
A dark nightmare...
That's all she'll say. But why?
Why is this young girl
traveling by herself?
I really think we've all had
enough sightseeing for one day!
Find us a place to rest!
What do you mean a place
to rest? We've got work to do!
Or have you forgotten
about our mission?
[GREEVUS]
Duty is important,
but a warrior must be
rested in order to succeed.
Greevus, you're so right!
Right, Neese?
Well... Um... I guess so.
I guess you're right.
The first thing we'll do
is find an inn where you
all can get some rest.
All right!
I can finally practically feel
the warm bath water right now!
And after that, I'll go
to see Governor Randal.
But Spark. You really could
use some rest as well.
Captain, let's relax
for a while.
No, I cannot rest until I
recover the Soul Crystal Ball.
That is my mission, after all.
You should know that
any thief worth his name
would never hold on to stolen
treasure for very long.
[horse whinnies]
[SPARK]
I am knight in training Spark.
I'm under orders
from King Kashue
to pursue a band of thieves.
My name is Randal. I'm the
royal governor of Hiruto.
I've heard of you.
And how you managed to escape
from the Dark Elves' trap.
Yes... But the thieves
still managed to get away.
[RANDAL] Whatever the case,
I've stationed soldiers
around the perimeter
of the city.
Although I doubt that we'll
ever be able to catch them...
[SPARK]
Is something wrong, sir?
[RANDAL]
You haven't heard?
Of course, how could you have?
Marmo and Alania have joined up.
[gasps]
You mean--!
We're at war.
King Kashue has already ordered
the entire army of
Flaim into battle.
[gasps]
[RANDAL] The king has set
out to Alania in order
to take command of
the first battalion.
We in Hiruto have sent 100
knights and 500 foot soldiers
to join the fight.
Because of that,
we can't give you full support.
We will, however,
do what we can.
[SPARK] We're finally at
war with the Marmo...
And where am I? Stuck out
here on a hopeless mission
in the middle of nowhere.
[RANDAL]
I know how you feel.
[gasps]
I was a top aide to King Kashue
during the War of Heroes.
And was fully prepared
to face the Marmo again.
But the responsibilities
of a royal governor
preclude him from
going off to war!
Governor...
[RANDAL] However, Spark,
no matter where you are
or who you're with,
battle will find you.
You understand?
[SPARK]
Yes, sir.
[LEAF] Spark really didn't have
to put us up in such a nice inn!
He's taking so long.
H-He must be really tired, too.
[NEESE]
You're right...
Hey! You ladies really
have a nice room!
C'mon! Don't you know
you're supposed to knock
before you come in?!
Oh, yeah. I keep forgetting
my mercenary manners.
Hey, Leaf, would you
take a walk?
You go with her, Neese.
[NEESE, LEAF]
Huh?
I've got to teach Ryna here
a little lesson
in mercenary manners.
All right--
Hey, come on! What's the
big idea?! Why d--!
Lesson in manners, my foot!
Garrack!
[GARRACK]
Hmph. Now, then.
The first thing you
can do is hand me that
nasty little friend of yours.
[RYNA grunts]
[RYNA] I thought you
wanted to teach me
about mercenary manners?
If you really were a mercenary,
I'd be happy to teach
you everything I know.
However, I don't do the
same thing for thieves.
[RYNA]
Uh...
Boy, that Garrack's
got some nerve
treating me like a little kid!
Especially since
a Half-Elf like me
will live way longer than him!
I'll bet you that
Garrack probably just
has the hots for Ryna!
Right, Neese?
Um, uh... I really
wouldn't know about that.
[LEAF]
Hm...
[gasps]
Oh!
Hey, you wanna go find out?
Find out about what?
The wonderful course of love!
You want to, right?
Okay, come with me.
C'mon, let's go!
[NEESE]
Uh, Leaf?
[door slams]
[door creaks]
[ALDO]
Mm? Hm... Uh.
Didn't I just hear Miss Leaf
and Lady Neese talking in here?
The young ladies have
gone off to discover...
..."the wonderful
course of love."
Huh?!
I only wanna know one thing.
Why are you trying
to get so close to us?
So close?
If you're looking
to travel cheap, okay,
but if you're up
to anything else...
...you'd better start running.
If you wanna stay alive.
There's only one
thing I'm after.
and that's revenge
for Randy's death.
You expect me to believe that?
If you had to stand by and
watch your lover get killed,
I bet you would.
Besides, if I really
did run off,
it would betray the
code of the thieves.
I doubted you. I'm sorry.
Uh?
[RYNA]
Thank you.
But if I do find that you've
betrayed us in any way,
then I'll bury that dagger
right here, in your chest.
[RYNA]
I'll keep that in mind.
Well, then! Why don't
you get some rest?
Not so fast!
Now I want you to
answer a question.
Come on. I know
you're not a mercenary.
Now. Who are
you really, Garrack?
[GARRACK laughs]
What are you talking about?!
Do I look like anything other
than a mercenary to you?
Oh, I'm not saying
that I don't trust you...
...but I really wouldn't want to
see Spark betrayed, either now.
[GARRACK sighs]
But the others don't
need to know about this.
We thieves don't betray trust.
[LEAF]
Oh... Man...
What are they talking about?!
[NEESE] Are you sure we
should be doing this?
[LEAF]
Sure, I'm sure!
It serves him right
for kicking us out!
Okay, we can peek
in through here.
Hey, let's choose!
"Let's choose"?
[LEAF]
Yeah.
One of us holds the
other on her shoulders
while the other one gets to
climb up and peek inside.
Now, let's see who gets
to do the peeking.
B-But, Leaf...
This way it's
completely fair! Right?
Uh. Right...
Oh, and no magic, either!
Of course not.
Good!
This one!
--[footsteps]
--[ALDO] Lady Neese!
[NEESE]
Aldonova.
What are you doing out
here in the hallway?
You really should
be in your room.
Are you curious, too? Have you
come to sneak a peek, Aldo?
Why! I never would!
Lady Neese, come with
me right now!
[NEESE gasps]
Bye, Leaf!
Hey! Now I'll never
get to see them!
A nobleman?! Are you kidding?
Oh, don't give me that look.
Look at my face. Look at me.
You can tell I'm not
exactly a model nobleman.
I've heard of men like you.
Overseer mercenaries who
are placed in the ranks
to police the men.
I've also heard that you
don't hesitate to kill
those who break the law or
collaborate with the enemy.
Well, it really
isn't that unusual
for a soldier to lose his
life on the battlefield.
And you do that, Garrack?
My current job is to protect
our incredibly eager,
young captain from danger.
You mean...
Yeah.
There's a chance he could become
the king of Flaim someday.
Assuming he doesn't get
himself killed first.
Those are King Kashue's
real intentions,
and that's the reason he
gave me this assignment.
It's pretty much
a losing battle--
taking care of our
captain is no easy job.
You seem to be enjoying it.
It's not easy to
leave him alone.
Believe me when I tell
you he's one strange bird.
[laughs]
What do you mean?
Well, he seems to
attract outcasts
and misfits like you and me.
And they say you're judged
by the company you keep.
[ALDO] Lady Neese,
do you really have to go?
[NEESE]
Mm.
Does Master Slayn
know about this?
Yes. My Mother, too.
They both know.
And I think they both understand
why I'm making this journey.
Yes, but, uh...
Why can't you understand
that this is a problem
I must face on my own?
Ever since the Soul
Crystal Ball was stolen...
No...
My fate was decided the
moment I had that nightmare.
Nothing will ever be the same.
Oh, Aldo. You know
that I am the door.
[CHILDREN laughing]
And it's for kids like
this that I must succeed.
For the sake of all of Lodoss...
Sorry about that!
Thanks! Bye!
Time for dinner, kids!
Come inside!
[CHILDREN laughing]
[ALDO]
Lady Neese...
To my eyes, you are just
a normal little girl,
no different
than these children.
By the gods, why?!
Why has such a terrible
fate been decreed
for this innocent little girl?
[SPARK]
What am I doing?
I can't take action as a knight,
and I can't join the
battle against the Marmo.
[BOY A]
Ha, ha! I'll get you!
[BOY B]
Oh, no you won't!
What the hell am I doing?!
[BOYS]
Huh?
[gasps]
[LEAF] Spark, you've got
to do something about this!
You are the captain, right?!
Uh! What's going on?
[growls]
Aldo and Garrack have
turned me into an outcast!
This is not going to
help develop teamwork!
Uh. What are you talking about?
And what are you
doing here anyway, Leaf?
Isn't your room over there?
It was! Until Garrack
threw me out because
he wanted to teach Ryna a
lesson in mercenary manners!
It's not like I don't know
what he's really teaching
her about in there!
What are you...? Uh...
Uh. Why don't you mind
your own business?
There are some things
a captain shouldn't see.
You're right! That's why you
should order me to check it out!
I know you want me to.
Now, hold on you!
[LEAF]
Hey!
[SPARK]
Uh. Sorry about that.
Captain. That was kind
of forward of you.
Uh! Don't be ridiculous!
[RYNA]
What's all the commotion?
[SPARK] Uh... It was, uh...
I-It was nothing at all!
There's nothing for
you to worry about.
[RYNA, GARRACK]
Mm?
Yeah, there's nothing
to worry about.
We know that you and
Garrack are in love!
[SPARK, GARRACK]
Huh?
Hey! What's that
supposed to mean?
Now, now! There's nothing to
be embarrassed about, Ryna.
Right, Spark?
Now that's enough!
There's absolutely
nothing going on!
First of all, this muscle-bound
ape is not my type!
Well, excuse me for
having a physique.
My muscles happen to
be my best feature!
What have we here? Is it a
lover's quarrel already?
[grunts]
What's the big idea?!
Just shut up!
It's your fault for starting
up irresponsible rumors
about us in the first place!
[LEAF] Oh, yeah?
Well, you were the one
who threw me out of my room!
[GARRACK] So, you're saying
this is my fault?!
[SPARK]
Would you both just cut it out?!
You're acting like
a couple of kids!
[GARRACK, LEAF]
Get lost!
[GREEVUS] Let them do as
their hearts direct them.
If you interrupt,
bad feelings will
remain between them.
[GARRACK, LEAF chattering]
[sighs]
What did I do to deserve this?
[NARRATOR] At that moment,
news that the Dark Elves
had been sighted to
the south of Hiruto
reached Governor Randal,
who quickly dispatched
troops to track them.
Upon hearing this,
Spark and the others
soon joined the pursuit.
[SPARK]
Hurry up! Let's go!
[GARRACK]
Are we really going?!
[LEAF] At this rate
I'll never get any rest!
Where's Aldo?
[ALDO]
Right here.
Huh?! Huh...?
I'm coming along with you.
Uh, Neese, I don't
think you really know
what you're in for here.
That's enough! We're not going
to be traveling anymore!
This is war!
That's right.
And Lady Neese's holy magic will
be most useful to us in battle.
Please, Spark.
Aldo, this is not her fight.
It may not be my fight,
but it is my destiny...
...so it becomes
my fight as well.
[SPARK]
Huh?
No matter what you say,
I'm coming with you.
[LEAF]
I bet the other pursuit team
already found the Dark Elves.
[RYNA]
I hope not.
I wanna avenge Randy's
death with my own hands.
[GARRACK]
Yeah...
[SPARK] I must focus on
completing my mission now.
It's the only thing that--
[PARN]
Don't become a man who lives
only for the duty given
that's given to him.
[SPARK] A man who only
lives for his duty. Huh.
[GREEVUS]
There they are!
[SPARK]
Huh?!
[GREEVUS]
It's them.
[ALL gasp]
I'll go on ahead!
Master Spark!
Now we've got a captain
who's really worth protecting!
[RYNA grunts]
[SPARK yells]
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've been
waiting for, the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
[NEESE humming]
Ah! The weather's so nice,
it's a perfect day
for a picnic! Right?
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Mm-hm!
[SPARK]
Come and get us, Dark Elf!
Huh?
I shall defend Neese's cookies
and become a knight of Flaim!
Is this getting old yet?
[NEESE] Want to join
me for lunch, Spark?
Huh?
These plums are great!
Man! What kind of mission
did I get stuck with?
[NEESE] I've got some
okaka rice balls for you!
Rice balls?!
I'll be right there!
Okaka, okaka...
Well, down the hatch!
[DARK ELF] Heh, heh, hey!
Big catch! Big catch!
One basket of cookies,
comin' up!
[SPARK]
Hold it, you cookie thief! Ahh!
Get... off... you...!
I'll never let go of
these cookies, you thief!
Let go, I said!
No way!
I said let go!
And I said no!
[yelps]
Uh? I didn't think
the weather report said
it would be
raining cookies today.
Hey! Why did he get to eat
the cookies there, huh?!
It' just ain't fair!
[SPARK]
Oh! Those precious cookies!
There goes my dream
of becoming a knight!
[DARK ELF]
Hey, hey! I'm outta here.
Oh, how could this happen?!
Now I'll never get
my own series!
I'll be a knight
in training forever!
[sniffs]
Hey, what's that smell?!
[NEESE]
The temperature's perfect!
This is so convenient.
With all the ingredients
and this little dragon here,
I can bake all
the cookies I want!
Thanks, Little Dragon!
All the cookies she wants?!
Then why am I even
on this mission?!
This bites...
[ALL]
We'll be seeing you!
[NEESE]
"Marfa, mother of the Earth.
Grant your miraculous
power to this young hero."
In the heat of the
battle to recover
the stolen crystal ball,
no one notices the approach
of another evil shadow.
Next time,
on Record of Lodoss War:
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"Nightmare...
The Creeping Dark Power."