There it is... Conquera!
[thunder cracks]
[NEESE gasps]
Where am I?
[WAGNARD] "Ladeera ve Kardis.
Vanna dol gellu deldo vir!
--Ladeera vanna dol!
--[NEESE screams]
Ar-day del ra Kardis!
Marda suda vegloss!
Ladora ladora dil dis!
Ladeera ludora Kardis!"
[growls, chuckles]
And now, it is time to wake up.
Arise, soul of Naneel,
queen of the dead,
who sleeps within the Doorway!
Let this unspoiled body call
the Destroyer to life...!
[gasps, grunts]
[gasps]
[NANEEL chuckles]
[NEESE gasps]
[NEESE gasps, shrieks]
I'll be there soon,
Neese. Hang on.
All right, everyone. Stay alert.
[GARRACK] What the hell is this
place? Some kind of a maze?
Damn... Which way?
Leylia.
[LEYLIA gasps]
[SPARK gasps]
[LEYLIA whimpers]
What are you feeling, Leylia?
The dark power is growing even
stronger... We've got to hurry.
The Destroyer's resurrection
is almost complete.
Unless you can tell us where
Neese is, it won't help!
In the meantime, she could be--!
Shut up!
I... I'm so sorry...
We must rely on your
powers now, Leylia.
So, please, try to
locate our daughter.
[LEYLIA breathes heavily]
[LEYLIA]
Neese...
[LEYLIA gasps]
She's that way.
Let's go!
[SPARK] The resurrection
is nearly complete?
If that's true,
then Neese is... Neese!
[gasps]
Sir Parn, what is it?
[gasps] What's wrong, Parn?
It's him, Deed.
[SPARK gasps]
[footsteps]
Huh. I really didn't think
you'd make it this far.
So, it will come down to
you and me once again.
[thunder cracks]
It's Ashram.
[gasps] Ashram?
The black knight...
At least we can settle
things before it all ends.
[grunts]
No!
Parn, there's no time!
Saving Neese must come first!
[GARRACK] Forget about that guy!
Let's get a move on!
You must forgive me, Slayn.
Please, help Spark.
Parn...
[PARN] Spark, I promise
I'll come to you later.
Now, go with the others.
But, Sir Parn!
[GREEVUS]
Spark.
[gasps]
These two heroes have
been battling each other
for a long time.
There is nothing we
can do to stop it.
That's not a good reason.
We cannot wait here anymore.
We must move on and see our
duty through to the end.
[SPARK groans]
Hey! Uh.
What should I do? Uh...
Parn... and Sir Ashram.
You'll go to him later?
Ha, if you live.
[growls]
Emperor Beld's great
dream is dead.
My ambitions burned
in the cauldron
of Fire Dragon Mountain.
My only purpose now is to lead
my people away from Lodoss.
And to do battle with a
free knight one last time!
[BOTH yell]
Do not interfere!
[PIROTESS] You'll have
to get through me first!
"Spirit of the wind, Sylph...
Rain down like arrows on
this servant of darkness."
[PIROTESS]
Now die!
[PARN yells]
[ASHRAM yells]
[swords clanging]
Oh, I'm scared....
Can this be the will
of Myrii as well?
[grunting, yelling]
All this for the sake of Lodoss!
For the sake of Lodoss,
to save it!
We fight just battles for peace!
You don't know anything!
How could you possibly
understand the hardships that
we've been forced to endure on
this monster-infested island?!
[ASHRAM growls]
[ASHRAM]
You're too self-righteous
to know the truth!
We only invaded Lodoss because
we had no other choices left!
"Just" battles... Yah!
[ASHRAM]
And then Wagnard comes along
with this ridiculous
scheme and ruins
whatever chances we
might've had on Lodoss!
Our rivalry...
is no longer relevant.
Parn!
[ASHRAM yells]
No!
[PARN yells]
[gasping]
[thunder cracks]
[thunder rumbles]
[gasps]
[MAAR whines]
So, what're you
planning to do now?
I shall lead the people
of Marmo out to sea.
And together, we shall
find a new land.
[gasps] In search of a new land?
I cannot think of a
single kingdom on Lodoss
that would actually welcome
the people of Marmo.
[ASHRAM] When Wagnard's
spell is complete,
this island will
no longer exist.
I must do whatever's necessary
to preserve the lives
of my people. The good,
hard-working people of Marmo.
And no matter what
trials we may face,
I am determined to
see this through.
We will build a new kingdom,
and we shall thrive.
This would make a great ballad.
"The song of Sir Ashram."
He's such a hero.
[ASHRAM] You and I shall
never meet again.
Farewell, Free Knight.
Wait for me, my lord!
Fare thee well, Black Knight.
[DEEDLIT]
Parn?
[laughs]
In the end, I really didn't
have to beat Ashram.
Right.
And maybe that's the
point of all of this.
Ashram and I both have
many goals to live for.
And as long as we can achieve
them, then winning a sword fight
doesn't really matter.
Still, that didn't stop you
two from fighting, Parn.
Ashram said it himself once.
As long as he and I live,
our battle will never end.
[HOBB] True. The real
battle is yet to come.
Although you may never
again fight with him,
you and Ashram will continue
to battle as you both lead
your people as kings.
But I don't have what
it takes to be a king.
[HOBB] Here, let me cast
a healing spell for you.
It's not serious, Priest Hobb.
And I think your time has come.
[HOBB]
Huh?
I want to thank you from
the bottom of my heart
for all of your valuable help,
but it's clear to me that
your path is headed in
a different direction.
Parn...
It's written all over your face.
In order to confirm
your faith in Myrii,
you must continue to
seek out true heroism.
My battle will soon be over,
but Ashram's struggles
are just beginning.
For the sake of
the people of Marmo,
Ashram is setting out into a
world he knows nothing about.
That's the work of a true hero.
Sir Parn, I... I'm happy
beyond all words.
It's been an honor to have
served a great hero like you.
And now, you're allowing me
to pursue my own
calling once again.
Ah... Myrii, great God of War,
I thank you, Lord!
Huh... He's gonna get to
watch history happen...
Hah! Well someone's got
to write a song about it!
Let's go, Parn. If we hurry,
we can still help them.
[PARN] You're right.
We've taken a lot of time here.
Let's go, Deed.
Um... Where's Maar?
Maar!
[MAAR]
Hey! Wait for me!
What's with him?! He panics at
the slightest sign of danger!
But he's just too curious.
[MAAR] Don't forget me!
I'll see you again someday!
[MAAR]
Hey! Wait up!
[GARRACK, ALDONOVA grunt]
Where are we?
Hey, what's going on?
Is this some sort of dead end?
Forgive me, Lady Leylia,
but are you certain
that this is where
you felt the evil?
This is where I felt them...
The evil presence is strong,
but it may be a trick.
I just don't know...
[GREEVUS growls] There must
be some clue around here.
Everybody, look for something.
What do you mean, "something"?
[SPARK] There's probably
a secret passage
that leads to Wagnard and Neese.
We can't afford to
waste any more time!
Now I want you to check every
wall seam, every column!
There must be a way in!
[GREEVUS growls]
I'm guessing if
there's a trigger,
it's gotta be right here.
Why would anyone hide
something in a place
where everyone would
look for it, Garrack?
Hey, you! I don't need
any of your wisecracks!
Now help me!
[SPARK] Damn... This can't
just be a dead end.
If we don't hurry,
then Neese will be--
[rumbling]
[gasps]
An earthquake!
[LEYLIA]
No, this is...!
No! The Destroyer must
be coming back to life!
Oh, no! We're too late! Neese!
[yelling]
[WAGNARD] "Ladeera ve Kardis...
Vanna dol gel deldo vir...
Ladeera vanna dol
deera aldee dis."
Ladeera ve Kardis!
Vanna dol gel deldo gah!"
[NEESE screams]
[whimpers]
[NANEEL giggles]
[NEESE]
No...
[NANEEL giggles]
[screams]
Yah... ah!
Damn it! What the hell
is going on here, Ryna?!
[gasps]
[RYNA]
What's happening, Garrack?!
Garrack! It's right
underneath you!
Yeah? Well, that's it, then!
Let's just get this
thing outta the way!
[grunts]
[yells]
Come on!
[gasps]
[SPARK gasps]
[WAGNARD yells]
[chuckles]
The power... This is the power
of Kardis the Destroyer!
And now, I shall rule the dead!
Magnificent! Magnificent!
[WAGNARD laughs]
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've
all been waiting for,
the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
Looks like you're
over your cold.
Yeah, I wasn't really that sick.
And, wouldn't you know?
We're really close
to Big Dragon Mountain.
Really?
[NEESE]
Freakin'-a right.
You're not kidding now?
[NEESE]
We're almost there.
[ASHRAM] Where the hell is
that Dark-freakin'-Elf?!
I ordered him to get those
cookies no matter what!
I got none!
In that case,
I'll get them cookies for
you myself, Lord Ashram.
What?!
Get a load of dis!
"Tiny-friggin'-spirits
of invisibility,
let thy form become my form!
Boo-boo-bee-doo!"
Un-freakin'-believable! You
gotta teach me how to do that!
[PIROTESS]
Sure thing there, Ashram.
Whoa! Hey! What the hell's
freakin' happening here?!
[NEESE screams, groans]
What're you doing?
Something's yankin' my cookies.
[SPARK]
Hey! Thought so! Hee-hee!
All right!
[PIROTESS] What're you--
Blue-haired bastard!
[ASHRAM] Get your freakin'
hands off my freakin' broad!
That broad is mine, got it?!
[SPARK screams]
What the hell is that thing?!
It's a ghost!
[inhales, roars]
[ASHRAM]
Ouch.
That freakin' hurts.
[PIROTESS] Ashram, take your
freakin' cape off, quick!
[ASHRAM]
Holy smokes! Retreat!
[PIROTESS]
Freakin'-a!
[BOTH]
Huh?!
Sir Ashram, your ass!
What about my ass?
Wah!
Don't look at my ass! You
didn't see anything, did you?
[PIROTESS]
Ew!
What was that all about?
Yeah, like I should know.
[LITTLE DRAGON squawks]
[NEESE]
Let's get the hell outta here.
[SPARK]
I'm with you.
I can't freakin' believe it!
She saw my heinie!
[NEESE, SPARK]
We'll be seein' you!
[SPARK]
The Destroyer's terrible powers
unleashed on the dark island.
As we move to the final battle,
Wagnard's terrible magic
takes its tragic toll.
Can a hero's sword cut
a path to the future?
What will be the fate of Lodoss
when all of this is over?
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War :
Chronicles of the
Heroic Knight :
"Destruction...
The Evil God Released."