[NARRATOR] The Era
of the Gods was closing.
Their once eternal rule
had come to an end.
The heavens trembled as the
armies of Falis, God of Light,
clashed with those of Falaris,
God of Darkness.
Their perpetual battle
ensued; the earth wept.
The seas boiled.
In the end, each side
had but one survivor:
Marfa, goddess of creation,
and Kardis,
goddess of destruction.
They met in a final battle that
echoed to the ends of the earth.
[NARRATOR] When it was over,
a new land was born,
broken away from
the rest of continent.
And the last flames of
the once invincible forces
of the goddesses
of light and dark
flickered and died away.
Thousands of years
have passed.
And now, the land to the south
of the continent of Alecrast
has become known as,
"Lodoss - The Accursed Island."
The way that you
embrace me with your
strong and powerful arms
Your haunting words keep me
close to everything about you
Romantic in ways
in ways that almost
tear upon my heart
Can't let you go
Don't you know?
Io sono prigioniera
A captive in
your gentle hands
A prisoner of
your soulful eyes,
your special smile
will never part
If the morning sun
should free me
It really wouldn't let me go
I'd still be caught
inside your love
Can't rise above
the chains of your heart
[eerie music plays]
[WOODCHUCK] So, this is the
Dwarves' Great Tunnel, huh?
There was a time
when you could buy
dwarf goods here
for a nice price.
Yes, indeed, you could.
There were many skilled dwarf
craftsmen who lived here.
[GHIM sighs]
A long time ago...
Yeah... Hey, now lemme
get this straight:
we gotta go through here to
get to Wort's place, right?
There are safer paths
we could take, Woodchuck,
but you must know by now
we haven't got the time.
Ew, it smells so moldy...
[GHIM] Then stay behind
if you don't like it!
Elf complaints aren't welcome
in this sacred place!
--How dare you?!
--[GHIM growls]
Ghim! Deedlit! Stop it!
If we don't get
to Wort's place soon,
all of Lodoss
could be in danger!
But he started it!
I'm not gonna put up with
any more of your nonsense!
Now, no one here is gonna
force you to tag along.
Leave, for all I care!
Excuse me!
[ETOH] This is neither the time
nor the place for an argument!
[thunder cracks]
[gasps]
--[ALL gasps]
--Hyah!
Hah!
[GHIM growls]
[yelps]
[wails]
[WOODCHUCK yells]
[ETOH]
Wood!
Hey, Parn! Get inside there!
All right! Move it!
"Omnipotent power,
creator of all things,
forged by the gods
from eternal chaos,
throw off these false garments
and reveal thy true forms.
Creators of all things,
become a shield to protect me.
Great protectors,
do not allow those
who will destroy your good
works to do their bidding
in this sacred place."
"Use me as your weapon
against these evils..."
Ooh, this would
fetch a good price...
...if it were finished.
Ooh! [giggles]
How beautiful!
Does it suit me?
I'm not going to
answer that right now!
I think it's really nice.
Thanks, Etoh.
--[rustling]
--Who's there?!
[footsteps]
Well, one thing is certain...
I know now that some evil
presence is trying to block us.
[KARLA] "None may
escape time's march."
Or so they say.
Has it really been so long...
...since the great battle in
the depths of the Labyrinth?
Who are you?
[KARLA] Was it not you
who vowed to protect me?
Before you charged
that Demon King,
my dear Wort.
[WORT]
Huh?
[KARLA]
Ah, yes...
The memories surface within you
of your companions,
the Six Heroes.
Silence!
What's a body?
Merely a dress to be worn
or discarded with time?
How much further is it, Slayn?
I don't know; we've just
got to trust Ghim on this.
Well, well, what did you expect?
The size of the dwarves'
Great Tunnel is legendary.
Oh, just get us out, Ghim!
I don't wanna end up losing
my head down here, ya know?
Relax, Wood, this is
a tunnel, not a maze.
If we keep moving,
we'll make it out.
[WOODCHUCK]
Phew!
Of course it takes longer
with a dwarf leading the way.
But what does an elf know
about these things anyway?
This place is really
giving me the creeps.
[DEEDLIT gasps]
Ooh!
[giggles]
No! Don't touch that!
[yelps]
[PARN]
Deed!
--Here, take my hand!
--Help me!
[BOTH yell]
--[ETOH] Parn!
--It's too late.
Deedlit!
[FAHN] You're going to seek
out Wort, the Great Sage?
[PARN]
Yes, Your Majesty.
Kannon and Alania
have already fallen
to the Marmo forces.
Valis is our last stronghold.
[FAHN] Wort may tell you
what you want to know,
but there's no guarantee
you'll make it back safely.
[PARN]
I know, Your Majesty.
But only the
Great Sage can tell us
what we need to know
about that witch Karla.
That--That armor...
This suit of armor
belonged to my father.
He was one of your
knights, Your Majesty.
[FAHN gasps]
[MAN]
King Fahn.
[FAHN]
King Kashue?
I'm impressed
with that boy Parn.
He's got good eyes on him.
[FAHN] I never thought I'd
meet the son of Tessius.
No. Deep down,
I knew I would.
Tessius?
[FAHN] I never so
cursed my position
as I did at that time.
[FAHN] Parn...
Please return safely.
[PARN]
Where do you think we are?
It looks like we're
in some sort of...
...secret hall.
What's that?
[DEEDLIT]
Oh, don't you know?
[giggles]
Look!
[PARN grunts]
Come on,
we've already
wasted enough time.
Let's just get outta here
and try to find the others!
Huh?
What's the matter?
--Look at this.
--[DEEDLIT] Hm?
It's--
It's part of a mural, I think.
Wait a sec.
"O great spirit of the light,
mother that nourishes plants,
come to me."
What the--?
I think I've
heard about this story.
The time of the
final battle had come.
Falaris, God of Darkness,
led an army of a thousand
ancient dragons and evil gods
against Falis, the Supreme.
It was a vicious battle.
Falis, and his
forces of light,
against Falaris's
army of darkness...
In the end,
the gods were destroyed
by their own great power.
It's a very old legend.
[PARN] They were destroyed
by their own power?
[DEEDLIT] I suppose it means
they grew too powerful
for their own good.
If they were
really that powerful,
a war probably
wasn't necessary, huh?
Keep talking like that
and you'll never
be a real knight, Parn.
Uh-- Yeah, well--
Um, I, uh--
You humans
don't make any sense.
But I guess that's what
makes you so charming.
[giggles]
[SLAYN] "To my staff,
I call the power
to turn back
the darkness."
[GROUP gasps]
Oh, hey, that's a handy
little thing to have around.
Come on,
we've got to save Parn!
Don't worry, he's got
the elf girl with him.
Yep, the air currents
will help her
to find their way outta there.
Huh. I can't figure it.
One minute, ya hate her,
and the next,
you're all compliments.
Shut up! Only a human
would let his feelings
prevent him from recognizing
someone's special talents.
Brother!
"Sylph, spirit of the wind,
let thy currents
guide us to the surface."
"Powerful Sylph,
great spirit of the wind,
let thy currents
guide us to the surface."
I thank you, Sylph.
[WORT] So, Karla, once one
of the great Six Heroes,
now the feared Great Witch,
what are you up to now?
I trust you know
about the sleeping dragon
who lies at the exit
of the Great Tunnel...
...dear Wort.
[DEEDLIT]
Uh-oh. [gasps]
[PARN]
What is it, Deed?
[gasps]
[SLAYN grunts]
[WOODCHUCK]
Hey, what's the hold-up here?
[ETOH]
Something wrong, Slayn?
[gasps]
Hey, Deed.
Quiet! Not a word now.
[DRAGON growls lowly]
Go ahead and
make a break for it;
I'll stay behind
and handle him.
What are you, out of your mind?!
[gasps, groans]
[DRAGON roars]
[PARN grunts]
Quick, Deed!
What's its weak spot?
I'm not a dragon expert.
How should I know?!
[groans]
[growls]
[yells]
[PARN yelps]
[BOTH scream]
Huh?
Hey, Slayn!
[ETOH panting]
Are they all right?
For the love of--
--[GROUP yells]
--[DEEDLIT gasps]
[SLAYN groans]
--[ETOH] Slayn!
--[WOODCHUCK] You all right?
Man, that thing's
gonna end up eating us!
Well then, we'll just
have to eat him.
[PARN grunts]
You must help him! Ghim,
what are you waiting for?!
Silence, elf!
Don't tell a dwarf
how to fight his battles!
[gasps]
[PARN groans]
--Parn!
--[GHIM yells]
[growls]
[GHIM growls]
[hollers]
Ghim, no!
[GHIM yells]
[DEEDLIT]
Ghim!
[WOODCHUCK growls, grunts]
[PARN]
Now!
[yells]
[PARN]
Now's our chance! Run!
[GROUP panting]
Daylight! We made it!
The obstacle is cleared,
as I said. So?
[KARLA]
Let us wait.
That is why
I have come, after all.
As you wish, Karla.
It's no concern of mine.
I feel all of
Lodoss trembling.
[KARLA chuckles]
I know. I'm here to see that
fate will balance
the scales of history.
This is all that I desire.
[NARRATOR] The heroes'
journey has only just begun.
And before them lies an
unimaginable destiny.
Let all the wonders
come to me
The fantasy fills,
fills my heart
I'll never wander anymore
For all the love I have,
I have for you
All the spirits of the wind
Spread their magic
wings and fly
Racing at the speed of light
Through the valleys
and the passages of time
When we fell in love
Destiny
Now each night
will have no end
Our nights will never end
Eternity awaits
You and me
Now that you are here
We'll never be alone again
Stay with me, my love