[PARN]
Hm?
[SOLDIER A]
Here he comes!
[DEEDLIT]
Huh?
[SOLDIERS chattering]
That's him!
It's Shooting Star...
Finally...
Our enemy has come back.
And... he looks real mad.
That Ashram is
some slave driver!
He really expects us
to leave in two days?
Yeah! And I thought being a
pirate was gonna make me rich!
[flute playing]
[PIRATE A]
Who's that?
What the--?
What's he doing here?
Well, at least we got
something to look at. Right?
[chuckles]
[SHIRIS yells]
Who do you think you are?!
Well, that's that.
Hope you enjoyed the show!
What a girl. I'm scared!
You see? I told you, Orson.
I didn't need any backup!
[chuckles]
[ORSON]
You were right.
All right, then. Let's go!
[NARRATOR] At that moment,
Slayn and Leylia,
who stayed behind in Raiden to
gather a crew for their ship,
learned the shocking
truth from a sailor
who had fled a pirate attack.
Are you absolutely sure?
Do you know what you're saying?
Yeah... I saw it
with my own eyes.
The pirate ship is
really a military ship.
And Marmo's flag was
flying from the mast.
The Marmo... Do you think
it could be Ashram?
Oh dear! What should we do?
There is only one thing
that we can do, I'm afraid.
We must believe in our friends
and wait for help to arrive.
Parn and the others are
due to return any day.
[SLAYN]
I have a bad feeling about this.
Parn...
[roaring]
It's him, Deed.
Please be careful.
[roaring]
[KASHUE]
Now is the time!
Let's put Shooting Star
to rest right now!
Prepare to attack!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[KASHUE] Keep as much space as
possible between each company!
Don't underestimate
the dragon's flames!
Let's show that thing
what we're really made of!
Yes, sir!
Deed! I'll leave my
magical support to you.
Right, sir.
Now wait until you
can see him...
Right! But with this
much firepower,
I doubt even a dragon
would stand a chance!
I bet we'll pierce his heart
on the first attack!
[roars]
The wind... It stopped.
What's going on? Deedlit!
There!
Huh?!
What is it?
[screaming]
Are you all right? Deed!
Yeah, Parn!
Okay, here it comes.
It's too soon!
Wait for him to get closer
in before you fire!
[roars]
[screaming]
I'm gonna draw him in!
Deed, summon the spirits!
But Parn!
Cover Parn, men!
Hyah!
King Kashue... Parn...
[PARN] Over here, you! Come on!
That's it! Come and get me!
Now, fire! Fire!
Show that beast the
true honor of Flaim!
[roars]
[screaming]
[KASHUE]
Damn you!
Come on, Deed! Hurry up! Hurry!
[DEEDLIT]
This is the spot...
"Iruku, great king of the wind,
I call upon thy mighty power."
[DEEDLIT] "Make the wind
become your sword,
and strike the demon dragon
with your whirlwind!"
[roars]
The wind blew him away!
Now, you die.
This madness must stop.
[yells]
[KASHUE yells]
How dare you!
Feeble humans,
you will never kill me.
I shall destroy your cities.
A hundred humans shall die
for every scale you
have scratched.
I will kill every
last one of you.
[DEEDLIT]
Parn!
[PARN]
I'm... I'm all right...
[SOLDIER B] If only our army
had even one sorcerer...
We have lost...
An utter and complete failure...
[GRODER] Sir Ashram,
it appears some people
have infiltrated our defenses.
Infiltrators?
Yes. And by the way, Smeddy...
One of them will give you
a run for your money.
There's a woman with
them who is younger
and far more beautiful than you.
Can there really be
a woman like that?
It sounds too good.
Astar, what do you think?
Gaberra, don't get
your hopes up.
Any woman is beautiful
compared to Smeddy.
[snickers]
[GILRAM]
Smeddy has a beautiful body.
She's very strong.
That's what I think.
That's all right, Gilram.
A warrior has no
need for beauty.
Strength is all that matters.
And I'll prove
that to all of you.
[ASHRAM chuckles]
Isn't this interesting?
Coming here with such a
small force to attack us...
Are they that good?
Or do they simply
not know their limits?
Or could they be foolish enough
to be coming after me?
I will test them
with my own hands!
[ASHRAM laughing]
Looks like we're here.
What do you think
you're doing? Let's go.
[SHIRIS]
What am I...? Uh...
[CECIL]
Uh, sorry.
Isn't that just like them?
There's a fortune
sitting right here,
and they're just
gonna ignore it!
[CECIL]
Get going, you!
[MAAR] That's the
pirates' ship, all right!
No doubt about it!
[SHIRIS] Good! Now we can
dispose of these pirates
and take the ship for ourselves.
[ORSON]
Marmo...
Wha--?!
Huh?! It's a Marmo ship?!
But that means--
And that means... Oh, you don't
suppose Ashram's onboard.
[ASHRAM]
I...
...am honored.
To think that my name is known
even by common thieves.
The black knight...
He must be Ashram.
So that's the little girl...
[SHIRIS gulps]
Don't be afraid, Shiris.
It's just talk.
Don't worry about me.
I'm a warrior, remember?
I want to know who
sent them here,
so make sure you
don't kill all of them.
Priest Hobb!
"A humble servant calls
upon the name of Myrii...
Gather the heroes here and
grant us thy divine protection
in the coming battle!
Give us resolve of iron
and the courage of
a thousand armies!"
[chanting]
So this is the legendary
power of the War God.
[chuckles] And I can feel the
power welling up inside me.
[yells]
You know, you're not
half bad, little girl.
[SHIRIS] I'm not your "little
girl," and my name is Shiris!
You think you're
pretty good, don't you?
Do not underestimate me!
Parn is the one who
taught me how to fight!
"And now, let the
manna of all creation
become the fires
of destruction!"
Aw, you gotta be kidding!
This guy's a real monster!
Who are you? I'll wager
that you work for Kashue!
If you will not answer,
then you will die!
[ASHRAM] The Soul Crusher
is reacting to him!
Who is this man?!
[CECIL] There's nothing
left to say! Now die!
[yells]
You were hardly worth
the effort, young man.
[MAAR]
Enough! Enough! You beat me!
I said I was sorry!
[whimpering]
"Let the manna of all
creation remake the air.
Commit his heart to slumber."
But what are you going to--?
Don't tell me that you're
getting winded already,
little girl.
That's really bad form.
What a fool.
Gotcha!
That was a real
lousy move, little girl.
[ASHRAM] Surrender!
You know you cannot beat me.
[ASHRAM]
Who is this man?!
[SHIRIS yelling]
[ORSON]
Shiris!
[gasps]
[growling]
[HYURI]
Rage... Destroy...
Destroy everything!
[gasps]
No!
This guy is really strong!
[growling]
So that is your true power.
You were only playing
with me until now.
Now you must face the power
of the demon sword,
Soul Crusher!
[yells]
[ORSON]
Wait. Don't go. Not yet.
I still have to beat this man.
I must save Shiris.
I still need your power!
Don't do it! No, Orson!
Please, don't do it.
Don't let it take control...
of your heart...
Are you... all right?
Yes, I am. I'm okay, Orson.
You're okay...
[ASHRAM]
You've lost to me.
Now surrender quietly,
otherwise...
Spare them for they
are not to blame.
I am their... leader.
I was a fool to think
that an army of men
would be able to
defeat a dragon.
[PARN] A hundred
people for every scale...
Now he must be stopped
once and for all.
[DEEDLIT] Parn...
What are we going to do now?
[KASHUE]
Until that beast is dead,
I am not worthy of my title.
Shadam, I want you to
gather up the wounded
and see them safely
back to Blade.
[SHADAM] B-But Your Highness!
What about you?
You can't--
Stop.
We're going to need
some powerful sorcery
if we're ever going
to beat that dragon.
I'm going to Raiden
to see Slayn.
[NARRATOR]
King Kashue, Parn, and Deedlit
urge their steeds forward
as fast as they dared,
urgently racing to
the city of Raiden.
Meanwhile, Ashram and his crew
have set sail for
Blue Dragon Island,
taking Orson and
the others as well.
Oh, Shiris...
--Welcome...
--...to Lodoss Island!
What you've all
been waiting for...
...the second part!
[giggles]
[NARRATOR] Parn and his gang,
hoping to slay Shooting Star,
have traveled to the fire
dragon's feeding grounds.
[ALL yelp]
You made me bump
right into Deedlit!
Would you mind doing it again?
I wonder when Shooting
Star is gonna show up!
I can't wait!
Ah! Where is he?
I wanna show him my stuff!
[grunting]
Oh, Parn, you're so strong!
[PARN screams]
Uh, did I say strong?
[chuckles]
The fiendish Shooting Star,
better not mess with me.
I'm King Kashue of Flaim!
[laughing]
Can it be?
It's him!
Oh, he's so cute!
[chirps]
You call this a dragon?
Isn't he the cutest
thing you've ever seen?
Come on, Shooting Star.
Now I'll show you...
...the true might of Flaim!
[chirps]
What have you done to the king?!
Aw, come on! Don't cry!
Now the dragon rights people
are gonna come after me.
This situation calls
for some magical help.
[KASHUE whispering]
But... Uh...
[KASHUE]
Now go to it!
"I summon thee, Iruku,
great king of the wind!"
How do you like that, Dragon?!
[sneezes]
[BOTH]
Ouch.
Way to go, Dragon!
You're really hot stuff!
[sneezes]
[ALL]
We'll be seeing you!
[DEEDLIT] Defeat.
And now, a new battle begins.
Awakened from his long sleep,
the rage of the sea dragon
shakes the heavens!
The black knight's demon
sword lights the darkness!
And in the heart
of a berserker...
...a long-forgotten light
flares back to life!
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War:
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"Heart... Tears Reborn."