[yells]
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] To the south
of the continent of Alecrast
lies an island known as Lodoss.
Forged in the fierce
battle between Marfa,
the Goddess of Creation,
and Kardis, the Goddess
of Destruction,
Lodoss has come to be known
as "The Accursed Island."
And now, in a land whose history
is painted with the hues of war,
new ambitions are stirred.
[NEESE]
Why has a knight of Marmo
come to this far-off place?
What brings you to this
holy temple of Marfa,
Goddess of the Earth?
You know about that
sword, don't you?
From the very beginning,
it's brought nothing
but suffering.
It was first used by
the king of the demons.
The Soul Crusher
should be locked away
where no one can
ever retrieve it.
I did not come this far
for a history lesson about
my sword, Priestess!
I have a question for you.
Will you answer me truthfully?
I will not lie, however--
Very well. A simple answer will
reveal what I need to know.
I want you to tell me about
the treasure of the
ice dragon, Bramd.
Why do you need to
know about that?
[ASHRAM]
I am a greedy man
who wishes to take Bramd's
treasure for myself.
Long ago, the glorious
kingdom of Sorcery
entrusted the five
ancient dragons
with the Governor's Treasures,
appointing them guardians
for all eternity.
However, the ice dragon
Bramd had no treasure.
But... that means you
must have seen him.
[ASHRAM] Indeed. He gave
us a rather nasty welcome.
However, I'm absolutely certain
the ice dragon regrets that now.
[gasps]
What have you done?!
I can't believe you'd
actually attack and kill
a hibernating dragon,
or would you...?
It's been rumored
you are the one
who released Bramd
from his terrible curse.
As a reward for his freedom,
he gave you one of his
treasures. Is that so?
I sold off that treasure
to help pay for the upkeep of
this holy temple of Marfa.
[ASHRAM]
I see.
But any treasure that
could be traded for money
would be of no use to me.
I apologize for disturbing you.
[NEESE]
Who are you?!
[ASHRAM]
I am Ashram,
loyal servant of
Emperor Beld of Marmo,
the man who united
this accursed island.
And now I have a question
for you, Sir Ashram.
What will you do with
the Governor's Treasures
when you finally acquire them?
My late emperor's wish
is my only desire,
the meaning of my life;
for that, I must possess
the greatest treasure of all,
The Scepter of Domination!
[NEESE gasps]
[NEESE]
Times are changing once again...
And destiny threatens
to leave us behind.
[PRIESTESS A]
Mistress Neese,
who were they?
You must summon Leylia
back from Zaxon right away.
Have her bring her husband
and my granddaughter as well.
[NEESE] Again, I must
entrust one so young...
...with the entire
fate of Lodoss.
[WOMAN A] C'mon, Orson!
You're holding us up!
Our enemies won't run away...
As much as I wish they would.
Blood should not
be shed needlessly.
[MAN A] Helluva thing
for a mercenary to say!
[MAN B] He sounds like
he's scared of fighting a--
a village full of hayseeds!
[GROUP laughs]
Now look, Orson. We are
going to Zaxon to pick up
some overdue taxes that are
rightly due to Duke Raster.
I doubt we'll have
to fight anyone.
And if we do,
it won't be a big job.
Either they all pay up,
or we'll make them pay up!
You can save the
tough-guy act for the job.
Are we clear on this, Orson?
Duke Raster is giving
us a quarter
of everything we collect!
This is a sweet deal, and I'm
not going to let you blow it.
So try to show a little
enthusiasm for a change!
Why try? I'll never
get through to him...
If he's not up for this,
let's dump him!
But cowardly mercenaries are
in such high demand nowadays!
[BOTH laugh]
You may laugh, but I'll warn
you now not to rile him up.
When Orson gets mad,
he's not able to tell the
difference friend and foe.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[ORSON]
Hm?
[GROUP gasps]
We're here.
Okay, now we stick
to the plan. Right?
[ARTEEN]
Cecil! Cecil! Trouble!
Cecil! Cecil!
[CECIL]
What now, Arteen?
Strangers! I think they're
soldiers! At the gate!
They wanna speak
to a negotiator!
They want to see Slayn?
[ARTEEN] Yeah! They said
they were from Alania!
The king ordered them to
collect the taxes from us!
[CECIL grunts]
All right! I'll just have
to send them away.
[ARTEEN]
By yourself?!
[CECIL]
Hm...
You're right about that...
You'd better go get him, too.
[SHIRIS] Where's the
village representative?
Don't you know it's rude to
keep the king's agents waiting?
Sickles and hoes!
You call those weapons?
How could they be so gutsy
with only one sorcerer
in the village?
And a human one at that!
One little human sorcerer...
It's him.
[VILLAGERS murmur]
Are you the one in charge here?
I am, and I'll get
right to the point!
The village of Zaxon
belongs to no kingdom!
And the people of our
village govern themselves!
Duke Raster has
no right to tax us.
And you have no
right to be here.
Now then, please
take your friends
and go back to
where you came from.
Hmph! Pretty tough words
for a phony sorcerer.
Now tell me, what kind of
cheap tricks did you do
to win over these poor yokels?
What? Are you trying
to insult me?!
[SHIRIS] Well, at least
he's got enough brains
to know he's being insulted!
And if you do have brains,
think about this.
It will be no
trouble at all for us
to smash this two-bit village!
Okay, everyone.
Here he comes. Get back!
[CECIL]
"Manna of all creation...
Become the fires
of destruction!"
Perhaps we should back
off a bit more!
Yeah... like it'll reach.
[yells]
[GROUP gasps]
Ah, fire!
So what's the big deal?
He can make a fire spell.
They're not that much trouble if
you don't attack them head on.
Follow my lead.
[VILLAGERS cheering]
Well, now!
[SHIRIS]
He-- He is a real sorcerer!
They didn't tell us
anything about this!
Run for it, Orson!
Hah! You're mine!
[CECIL]
Huh? Where'd they go?
Damn! It's a trap!
[SHIRIS] I didn't think
you'd be stupid enough
to fall for one this simple.
Guess I was wrong.
What kind of magic
spell is gonna
get you out of
trouble this time?
[growls]
[SHIRIS]
Anyway, you're trapped now,
so why don't you drop that
sorcerer's staff, Mr. Slayn?
Drop it, I said!
Huh? I'm not him.
My name is Cecil,
and I'm the captain
of the village defense
forces while Slayn is away.
Huh? But no one told us
there'd be two of them.
Raster said there'd only be one.
[SHIRIS growls] It doesn't
matter who you are then!
The fact of the matter is that
you are still our hostage!
Even if you take me hostage,
the village of Zaxon
will never pay taxes
to finance Alanian wars!
Kill me if you want to!
You've sure got guts.
Whatever you wish.
Is it really necessary
to kill him?
I'm sure of it!
There's no way we can let him
get away with humiliating us!
[SHIRIS]
Come on!
If you're going to beg
for mercy, now's the time!
[DEEDLIT] The wind spirit
Sylph is protecting you.
You're safe now, Cecil.
Hey, come back!
Fire!
[CECIL screams]
[SHIRIS]
What the--?!
The wind spirits?!
But I didn't see
him cast a spell!
The sorcerer didn't do it.
The elf did.
[SHIRIS]
An elf?!
Come now, Cecil. Why are
you still so careless?
Deedlit!
[PARN]
Cecil! I'll take it from here!
[CECIL]
Parn!
You two can stop this right now!
If you don't,
I'll show no mercy!
[SHIRIS]
Parn... I've heard of you!
Aren't you the famous
free knight?
The great swordsman who
travels with the high elf?
He's good. Don't fight.
You stay out of this!
Hey, Parn! If you really wanna
fight me, you'd better hurry up!
And you guys, watch
for his magical friends!
Keep 'em back!
[yells]
"Gentle airs that
brings sleep..."
"Great sprit of the
free-blowing winds,
let the trembling
of the air cease
and make all sounds vanish..."
--Oh my--!
--Deedlit!
[CECIL]
"Manna of all creation...
Become the fires
of destruction!"
Hurry up, Cecil!
He's gonna kill me!
Deedlit, what did you do to him?
I cast a spell of silence,
hoping that it
might confuse him.
But even when all sound
vanished, he just kept going.
It's strange, but he didn't
seem disturbed by it.
[swords clanking]
Drop your sword.
There's no way you can beat me.
[growls] I'm not done!
[CECIL]
He's coming this way! Deedlit!
[SHIRIS screams]
[ORSON]
Shiris...
[SHIRIS]
Okay, okay. I accept it.
You beat me, Mr. Warrior.
Then you agree to
listen to me now?
Well since you've beaten me,
I really don't have
much choice now, do I?
Of course, you will
have to let me live.
That's not much of a condition
for an unconditional surrender.
[ORSON growling]
Orson?!
[SHIRIS] Quick!
Drop your sword! Orson's--!
[DEEDLIT]
Parn, run!
Parn!
Stop it right now, Orson!
I'm all right!
Orson! I'm telling you,
Nothing will affect him now.
I thought there was something
strange about him.
I'm sure now;
he's become a berserker.
A berserker?!
[DEEDLIT] That man is controlled
by the spirit of rage and anger.
The only things he
can feel now are rage
and the absolute need to kill.
What are you saying?!
[DEEDLIT]
The possession is so strong,
he cannot distinguish
between friend or foe.
He'll keep on killing
until his body falls apart.
I don't believe it!
If a guy like that
got into the village--
He must be stopped!
[DEELIT]
Parn!
[SHIRIS yelps]
[SHIRIS]
Orson, stop it!
Stop it!
No, Orson!
[clang]
[PARN] I see now. So,
this is a berserker, huh?
What are you--?!
[PARN] What are you doing?
Get out of here!
Why you! Hey, who said
I needed to be saved?!
[PARN]
This guy's strong...
Deed!
It doesn't look like I can
beat it with just my sword!
So it seems.
"Gentle spirits of the forest...
I pray thee, lend unto
me your strength!"
"Leprechauns,
spirits of confusion.
Shades, controllers of fear.
Disrupt the anger
that controls him
if only for a short time."
I think it's working,
Deed! Nice job!
"Spirits of enchantment,
spirits of chaos,
spirits of darkness..."
Orson! Can you hear my voice?!
Please wake up, Orson!
[DEEDLIT]
Parn, finish him!
[PARN]
Right, Deed!
No, wait! Don't kill him!
Move aside!
I won't let you kill him!
Look at him;
he's returned to normal!
He's not a berserker anymore!
Move!
I will not stand by and
let you kill my friend!
You won't let your
friend be killed, well...
We'll patch up your wounds.
You can tell us your story
when we get to the village.
[SHIRIS]
Orson. Orson, snapt out of it.
A long time ago,
Orson watched as
his older sister
was murdered before his eyes.
Since then, whenever he
sees a woman in danger,
he starts fighting
like a madman.
I know that you can't really
change your destiny.
But if that war hadn't happened,
perhaps Orson would
not be this way today.
Even though the War
of Heroes may be over,
it seems to me, there are
still some places in Lodoss
where its wounds have
not yet been able to heal.
By the way, have you decided
what you're going to do with us?
If you swear to us
that you and your friend
will never bother
our villagers again,
I will allow you to
go free this time.
[SLAYN] Oh, my...
Everyone's here already!
It's Slayn!
Welcome home, Master!
Is there anyone here who
can tell me what's happened?
Parn, you look a
little worn out.
Of course I am.
I was busy risking
my life for the village,
and, well, it kinda
tires me out!
You don't usually take Leylia
and Little Neese with you
when you go away, Slayn.
Hey, young lady,
where did you all go?
We went to see Big Neese!
She's my grandma!
You went all the way
to Marfa's temple?
Why, yes, that's right.
You see, I received an urgent
communication from Mother.
And I need your help, Parn.
[PARN] Not today,
Slayn. I need a break.
Save it for tomorrow.
Then I'll fight your
dragon or whatever it is.
You mean, you'll really
fight a dragon?
What a relief!
I was worried about what I'd
have to do to convince you,
but not anymore!
You're a lifesaver, Parn!
You did say a dragon,
didn't you?
[SLAYN] Yes. For the sake
of Lodoss. And at any cost!
--Welcome...
--...to Lodoss Island!
What you've all been
waiting for...
...the second part!
[giggles]
[NARRATOR] To the south of
the continent of Alecrast
lies the accursed
island of Lodoss.
It is covered by all
sorts of kingdoms,
both large and small.
[PARN grunting]
Parn is a free knight.
That means he isn't
bound to any kingdom.
[giggles] Right, Parn?
[DEEDLIT] If he swears
loyalty to one kingdom,
he can't help any others.
As a free knight,
you wanna help all people who
live on Lodoss, right, Parn?
[grunting]
Oh my, Parn! Once you set
your mind on something,
you don't notice anything else,
do you, Parn?
Well, I guess that's
why I, um... Oh!
Ooh, you love him! [giggles]
[DEEDLIT gasps]
Love! Love...!
Aw, Slayn!
What's wrong now, Deedlit?
Why did the spirit
of anger appear?
Uh, keep on fighting to build
that wonderful tomorrow, Parn!
Don't give up, Parn!
We're the heroes!
Pow-pow, Parn! Come join in!
[PARN]
Uh...
[BOTH]
Pow-pow, Parn! Pow-pow, Parn!
Go now, Free Knight of Lodoss!
So this is the free knight that
I've heard so much about.
Pow-pow, Parn!
I want you to fight
a terrible dragon
for the sake of Lodoss Island!
He's real tough! So be strong,
oh brave free knight!
Pow-pow, Parn!
Huh?
[DEEDLIT, SLAYN, SHIRIS, ORSON]
Pow-pow, Parn! Pow-pow, Parn!
[DEEDLIT]
Parn, you, too!
[PARN]
Me?
[ALL]
Pow-pow, Parn!
But what exactly
does it all mean?
That you'll never know
what'll happen next.
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
Pleased to meet you!
[ALL]
We'll be seeing you!
[PARN] A sudden mission to
become dragon slayers.
Neese, Priestess of
the Earth Goddess Marfa,
has entrusted Slayn
with this responsibility.
Now is the time to reveal
the dark memory
that has been kept
for 500 years!
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War:
Chronicles of the Heroic Knight:
"Dragon... The Guardian
of the Lost History."