[REONA] Fifteen years ago,
Emperor Beld started
what became known as
"The War of Heroes."
Since then, the Marmo have
controlled my father's kingdom,
using it as their
gateway to Lodoss.
But no more!
Today, our great
dream is at hand!
We shall retake
our home! Now go!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Uh! What the--?!
[HOBB singing]
[gasps] It's an enemy attack!
Battle stations!
[GARRACK] Out of the way!
Move aside! Move it!
[GARRACK yells]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
All right, men! Now we
attack their main force!
Follow me!
[SPARK]
Hey! Garrack, come on!
Our objective is the city
center! Now move!
Right, sir!
[panting]
[GARRACK]
Come on, Priest, move it!
That's easy for you to say!
[LEAF]
Coming through!
[GREEVUS]
Hey!
[yells]
[GRODER growls]
I cannot believe it...
[ASHRAM]
What is it, Groder?
[GRODER] Sir Ashram, the
free army is attacking.
They've penetrated
the city gate.
It has begun...
I never thought the enemy
would attack before
the reinforcements
from Flaim arrived.
I guess I misjudged them.
Even though they may
have attacked us first,
we still greatly outnumber them.
There's no reason why we can't
fight them hard and beat them.
[ASHRAM]
Hmm.
Gather all of our
troops together.
Defend the city
center at all costs.
[MESSENGER]
Sir!
[ASHRAM] Roodo was Marmo's
first foothold in Kanon;
our main artery into
the rest of Lodoss.
If Roodo falls, then...
[ASHRAM growls]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[DEEDLIT] "Sylph,
mighty spirit of the wind.
Become a violent whirlwind
and repel them."
[yells]
[yelling]
Remember your missions, men!
And do not delay!
[PARN yells]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Parn! We can handle these
Marmo dogs! Now go!
Smash their eastern sector!
[MAAR grunting]
All right! I did it!
Huh?!
[yelling]
[GARRACK yells]
[LEAF yells]
That's it!
Huh?!
Hey, Captain, the
first ones are mine!
No, Garrack! Wait!
[GARRACK growls]
Come on and show yourselves,
you lousy Marmo bastards!
[growling]
[gasps]
[growling continues]
Wh-What the hell
is that thing...?
Captain! [screams]
Garrack!
[grunting]
[growling]
[yells]
All right!
[SPARK yells]
[GREEVUS] Hmm... Maybe this
is more than just a toy.
[TROLLS growling]
[GRODER] They attacked
all of our positions
with the few troops
they had? Impossible!
[ASHRAM]
Trying to confuse us and prevent
the consolidation of
our forces... Clever...
Now Groder, I want you to take
our wounded and bring them all
down to the docks.
But... But sir! You mean...?
We still have people
back on Marmo.
For their sake, we cannot allow
our surrender in Kanon.
Pirotess, I leave
the rest to you.
[PIROTESS]
Yes, sir.
[GRODER]
But Sir Ashram!
"Great Spirit of Fire.
Spider of bright crimson!
Let your flames breathe
from within the enemy!"
[yelling]
[SPARK yells]
[PARN]
Spark!
Sir Parn!
You did it, Spark! Well done!
Sir.
The attack was a huge success.
Our scouts say that the Marmo
are already retreating.
We can't relax yet.
I want you and your group
to head back to the main force.
We've got to make sure
that Prince Reona's victory
over the Marmo is complete.
What about you?
What about... Well, I...
I've got some unfinished
business to take care of
with an old friend.
I'll see you later, Spark.
[SPARK]
Yes, sir! And please be careful!
Oh, great. Why does he
always have to run?
[SPARK] Almost there... The path
to Marmo is almost clear!
Wait for us, Neese!
[WAGNARD]
Hmph! Those fools...
No matter how desperately
you struggle,
it's too late. The preparations
for the destroyer's resurrection
are complete!
You're only wasting your time.
[WAGNARD laughs]
[PARN grunts]
All right, Ashram!
[BOTH gasp]
It's Pirotess!
Heh!
[yells]
[PARN grunts]
What?!
[PIROTESS laughs]
Look out, Parn! Up top!
[PIROTESS]
Hyah!
[yells]
[PIROTESS giggles]
[footsteps]
There!
[PIROTESS gasps]
"Great Spirit of
the Wind, Sylph.
Become a hail of
arrows and pierce
this servant of the darkness!"
That was a nice move.
Wait!
[PARN grunts]
All right, where
the hell is Ashram?!
[PIROTESS]
Heh.
[BOTH gasp]
It's Ashram.
An excellent job, Pirotess.
Sir.
Set a course for Marmo.
Man your stations. Sail on!
After all we've done in Roodo...
Are you sure about this?
Of course I am. Do you
really understand why
we came to Lodoss
in the first place?
[GRODER]
Sir?
You need subjects
to make a kingdom.
All I've ever tried
to do here was secure
a better place for
the people of Marmo.
Sir Ashram...
Ha-ha! Hey, we did it!
Ashram couldn't beat us,
so he turned and ran away!
[gasps]
That's it, then.
If the kingdoms of the
island of Lodoss reject us,
then so be it. But I still
have a solemn duty
to find a safe home for
the people of Marmo.
[ASHRAM] There's only
one path left for us.
We shall abandon
this accursed island
and set out on the seas.
The people of Marmo will
have a land of their own.
No, Maar. You are
wrong about Ashram.
He is a true visionary
and a leader.
[PARN growls]
[NARRATOR]
With Ashram's retreat,
the curtain fell on
the battle over Roodo.
Without leadership, the
remaining Marmo soldiers
lost their will to fight.
And with the city of Roodo
finally free of the Marmo,
Prince Reona proudly proclaimed
the rebirth of Kanon...
...and his rightful
place as its leader.
Uh?
[RYNA giggles]
[SPARK chuckles]
[NARRATOR] That night, King
Kashue and the army of Flaim
arrived at Roodo,
having completed their
long trek from Alania.
The joyous reunion
with Prince Reona
resulted in a new alliance
between the rededicated
kingdom of Kanon and the
desert kingdom of Flaim.
Highness! Welcome.
Parn! I'm sorry for the delay.
Defeating Duke Raster took
longer than I had anticipated,
but I've just signed a
treaty with Prince Reona
to join forces for
the sake of Lodoss.
I'm glad. But, Your Highness,
what has become of Alania?
[SLAYN] The new king Robess
has assumed full power there.
[PARN]
Slayn! And Laylia, too!
The new king has a whole
new government to set up.
We had to leave Cecil
behind to help him.
Flaim and Kanon...
Alania and Valis...
It looks like the great kingdoms
of Lodoss are finally uniting.
And the only exception is
the dark island of Marmo.
[BOTH gasping]
But I don't think there's
too much to worry about.
With so many of us
allied against them,
Marmo ambitions will
surely begin to wain.
I hope you're right,
Your Highness.
[SPARK]
Highness! I must speak with you!
[ALL]
Huh...?
I thought I ordered
you back to Flaim.
[KASHUE] What?! The two
keys and the Doorway
are now in Wagnard's hands?!
Our daughter...!
[ALDONOVA]
Oh, forgive me, Master!
Even though I was here
with her, she...
She... Oh, Lady Neese!
There was nothing
that you could've done
to prevent this, dear Aldonova.
Even if the circumstances
were different,
she would've wound
up on Marmo anyway.
It is her destiny
as the Doorway.
She could not fight it.
I'm sorry...
Even though we've got enough
men to go after them,
we haven't got the proper means,
because Ashram took almost
every available ship
when he ordered
the Marmo retreat.
Well, that means we'll
just have to wait
until reinforcements and ships
arrive from the holy kingdom.
But Highness, that's not
an acceptable option!
[KASHUE]
Hmm?
If the resurrection
ceremony is completed,
then Neese will... If I could
take just a small group with me
on one of the remaining ships,
then I swear to you
that I will save Neese and stop
the Destroyer's resurrection!
You can count on me to come
along and help you, Spark.
Anyway I can.
Sir Parn...
Heh. Well, I guess it's
been decided, then.
[gasps] Highness...
Here it is. Until we
can plan our invasion,
there's still much to
be done here in Lodoss.
Yours is the only group
prepared for this mission.
Now go, quickly.
[SPARK gasps]
I leave the entire future
of Lodoss in your hands.
[gasps]
Sir!
[WAGNARD]
Hmm?
Hmph!
I already know that
Roodo has fallen.
Now no one can stop
the tide of time.
So... tell me now, Grey Witch.
Who do you think
will win my game?
I'm still opposed to the
Destroyer's resurrection.
Therefore, I alone must
stop the tide of time.
[WAGNARD] You shall only serve
to bury the light of Lodoss
with your own hands. [chuckles]
All of you may continue on
with your useless struggles,
but I doubt the power
of the Grey Witch
will be able to
make a difference.
[KARLA] Should I fail, you may
do as you like, Wagnard.
The negotiations
are over, Karla.
[chuckles]
[NEESE gasps]
What do you want?!
It is time.
The holy altar to Kardis the
Destroyer awaits the sacrifice.
[sighs]
[laughs]
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've
all been waiting for,
the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
The young and not old free
knight Parn has appeared
once again to help Spark
and Neese prevent
the special cookies from
falling into evil hands!
Now, they find themselves
in a dangerous situation
thanks to the Dark
Elf's deadly trap.
Hey, huh? This wasn't my trap.
Why I oughta...
Ain't this freakin' great?
Just hangin' around...
Hey! Didn't I tell you to
bring those cookies to me?!
Huh...? I'm really
sorry there, my lord!
Huh...?
Ahh!
Boy, that was close...
What a freakin' moron...
Freakin' a right, Ashram.
[PARN]
Deed!
[BOTH gasp]
Ah! You came to save me,
didn't you?!
Oh, Dee! Dee!
Hey, I ain't her! Let go!
Hey! Get your
goodie-freakin'-two shoes hands
off my freakin' broad, okay?!
[PARN screams]
That broad is mine!
Dee! Dee! Dee!
Get this lame-ass off of me!
That's it! Now I'm gonna
cut you up, sissy boy!
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH grunting]
[yells]
[SPARK]
Not again!
[BOTH scream]
[LITTLE DRAGON squawks]
It's good to have a flyin' pet.
You can say that again.
[DARK ELF]
How 'bout a lift there, huh?
[ASHRAM, PARN shouting]
[DEEDLIT]
That two-timing bastard!
[ASHRAM] I'll murdalize you!
You get back here!
Thanks again, Little Dragon!
That was close!
[DEEDLIT] Get over here
you two-timing bastard!
[PARN screams]
[coughs]
Well, maybe I overdid
it a little...
[giggles]
[ALL]
We'll be seein' ya!
[SPARK] We finally made it
to the dark island of Marmo.
As we hurry through
the dark forest,
we are attacked by
demonic creatures,
a trap set by Karla,
the Grey Witch.
But I cannot slow down!
Not until Neese is safe.
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War :
Chronicles of the
Heroic Knight :
"Landing...
The Terrifying Dark Island."