[NARRATOR]
Light and darkness...
The final battle of the gods
climaxed in a clash between
Marfa, goddess of all creation,
and Kardis, goddess
of destruction.
At the end of their
fierce battle,
the stricken goddesses
had split the continent,
forming a new land.
Since then, people have come
to call this new continent
"Lodoss - The Accursed Island."
The way that you
embrace me with your
strong and powerful arms
Your haunting words keep me
close to everything about you
Romantic in ways
in ways that almost
tear upon my heart
Can't let you go
Don't you know?
Io sono prigioniera
A captive in
your gentle hands
A prisoner of
your soulful eyes,
your special smile
will never part
If the morning sun
should free me
It really wouldn't let me go
I'd still be caught
inside your love
Can't rise above
the chains of your heart
[panting]
Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah!
Ah, at the head of the column
with the strongest
knights in Valis.
So what've I got
to worry about!
Don't be foolish, Woodchuck.
In a battle, this would be
the most dangerous spot.
The enemy always attacks the
head of the column first.
Aah, you sound pretty sure
of yourself, Deedlit.
It's just basic tactics.
[WOODCHUCK]
I see.
[PARN chuckles]
Huh?
[neighs]
[KNIGHT A] King Fahn!
King Kashue's division
is under attack
by an army of creatures!
You must send help, sire.
[FAHN]
What of their main force?
There's no sign.
Curse him! Beld's using
those monsters!
An army of them?
The creatures are expendable.
There could be
thousands of them.
Tens and thousands
of those monsters.
Kashue's stranded!
[yelling, groaning]
Stand firm, men!
We won't lay down
to an army of animals!
They don't know
how to fight! Stand firm!
[yells]
[groans]
[KASHUE]
Prince Jester!
So, even the
great mercenary king
lacks eyes in
the back of his head!
[thunder cracks]
And so, the game begins.
[DEEDLIT] Is your
heart galloping faster
than your horse, Sir Knight?
I think you better
reign it in quickly.
Or it'll be of no use to you
when the time comes. [giggles]
A gift from my son...
for good luck.
[MARMO A]
What should we do?
If we allow them to join up,
they'll be an even
bigger threat!
[ASHRAM] The plan
is to drive our prey
into the hunting ground.
[ASHRAM] My lord, the prey
is almost in the trap.
[PARN]
King Kashue!
Parn, you're here!
[PARN]
Yes, sire!
It's Fahn!
[KNIGHT B]
We're boxed in!
[KNIGHT C]
Where are they?
[KNIGHTS chattering]
[neighs]
It's Beld!
[chuckles]
Hello, Fahn.
[KNIGHTS chattering]
[KNIGHT D]
They're behind us, too!
[WOODCHUCK]
What's going on?
Well, talk about
being a sitting duck.
Parn! Get ready!
[yelling]
Parn...
[SLAYN]
Go to him, Etoh.
But Slayn...
[SLAYN]
We can't stop it now.
Whether we're swept into
the storm or we avoid it,
it's all the same.
It wouldn't even matter if they
managed to win the battle...
...somehow.
[GHIM] "Lodoss will be saved
by war." Ridiculous!
[SLAYN] It would seem that
Karla believes otherwise.
But you and I have
our own battle to wage.
A very different
sort of battle.
[PARN]
You cursed witch!
[yells]
Did King Fahn give you
orders to slay me?
[PARN] You became
his enemy the minute
you sided with the Marmo!
[KARLA]
Shall I support Valis, then?
Wha--?!
It really doesn't make
any difference to me.
[PARN gasps]
[KARLA chuckles]
I must thank King Fahn
and my friend, Wort,
for allowing me to finally
meet my new pawns.
[PARN] Wort! Is that how
you feel about all this?!
[growls]
That boy may be
the one, after all.
[PARN yells]
[DEEDLIT yells]
[WOODCHUCK yells]
[yells]
[MESSENGER]
Princess!
We've just received word
from the battlefield.
The situation is grave.
I understand. Thank you.
[PARN]
It's him!
It's him...
[grunts]
[yells]
[groans]
You should know,
a sword is not a toy.
What?! A toy?!
Let me demonstrate
its proper use!
[PARN yells]
[DEEDLIT]
Parn!
[PARN yells]
[ASHRAM gasps]
[ASHRAM]
Wait.
I don't need you.
[DEEDLIT gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH gasp]
[FAHN]
Beld!
Where are you? Where are you?
Where are you?!
Come on, show yourself!
What are you? Afraid?
Surely you haven't
forgotten my face!
--[PARN] Come back here!
--[DEEDLIT] Parn!
[PARN gasps]
So the battle is finally
drawing to an end now.
[FAHN]
Beld!
Hey, Beld!
Beld! Beld!
Long time, Fahn.
The past is closed to us.
This is the only way left.
My old friend, Beld.
Very well, my old friend.
[BOTH yell]
[swords clashing]
Must this be our fate, Beld?
No matter what, you will
never have Lodoss!
Conquest of Lodoss
was never my desire!
Unification or conquest...
It is all the same!
[KARLA chuckles]
Lodoss will be neither
unified nor conquered.
[PARN gasps]
Your Highness!
[WORT]
Parn, you must stop Karla.
Huh?
[WORT]
Parn!
Come out here, Wort!
Even if this terrible war
should come to an end,
Lodoss will never
know true peace
while Karla is still alive.
[PARN]
What do you mean?
Karla believes that this war
is good for Lodoss.
And that means...
So, you're saying that
if I kill Karla,
I can put an end to this war.
That I cannot say
for certain, but...
...the death of Karla will
advert the tragedy to come.
A tragedy?
What do you mean by that?
Karla's strange. She doesn't
consider herself human.
After living for 500 years,
she's become unbalanced.
And although I tried,
I could not get her to
stop her destructive ways.
If she continues to interfere,
then all of Lodoss
will be faced with even
greater disasters to come.
In order to prevent this...
[WORT] Remove the circlet
from her forehead.
That is her true self!
[DEEDLIT]
Parn, what's wrong?
Now why did Wort--
[whooshing]
Age hasn't changed us much,
has it, my old friend.
Maybe not, Beld, but I'll live
long enough to see you dead!
[laughs]
My feelings exactly, Fahn.
[BOTH yelling]
[groans]
--[ALL gasp]
--[thud]
[ASHRAM]
Sire!
[BELD screams]
[KARLA] Lodoss will be neither
unified nor conquered.
[BELD screams]
There is evil about!
Quickly, take cover now!
[roars]
[growls, roars]
[PARN]
Sire!
Uh, uh, we can't
just leave him here.
[KASHUE] The dead return
to the soil of Lodoss.
That is the destiny
of all knights.
Such is the way... of war.
Nameless soldiers
are like dust, Parn.
Nobody will ever remember them.
Only those who earned their
names are ever remembered.
A gift from my son...
for good luck.
[DEEDLIT]
Parn...
It's just not right, Deed.
I swear, it's...
just not right.
[WORT]
You must stop Karla.
Or else Lodoss may face
an even worse disaster!
[NARRATOR]
A war without meaning.
A war that saved no one.
Alas, yet another battle
must be fought.
As he stood amidst
a sea of bodies,
the young man vowed to challenge
Karla, the Grey Witch.
Let all the wonders
come to me
The fantasy fills,
fills my heart
I'll never wander anymore
For all the love I have,
I have for you
All the spirits of the wind
Spread their magic
wings and fly
Racing at the speed of light
Through the valleys
and the passages of time
When we fell in love
Destiny
Now each night
will have no end
Our nights will never end
Eternity awaits
You and me
Now that you are here
We'll never be alone again
Stay with me, my love