[GUARD A] Halt! The king has
declared a state of war!
No one is allowed into Valis
under any circumstances.
Ya think you can stop us?!
[gasping]
Calm down, Garrack.
We have been sent here by
order of the king of Flaim.
I have a message for King Etoh.
You've come from Flaim?
Then, please, forgive us.
I know your security
is important,
but are things really
that bad here?
Yes, they are, I'm afraid.
The Marmo just won't let up.
Would your message be about
Flaim sending reinforcements?!
[gasping]
Will King Kashue himself be
leading the troops from Flaim?
[GUARD C] When are they
going to get here?!
[SPARK] I never knew
things were this bad...
Valis really needs help.
It's very quiet, Priest Greevus.
Yes, it is. The people
are probably afraid
to come out of their homes.
[SPARK]
I think you're right.
Valis's army must be having
a really tough time
trying to fight off the Marmo.
Just like them. And now
they're all counting
on the army of Flaim
to come and save them.
[RYNA] But King Etoh
has a good reputation.
Could it be that
the people of Valis
have lost faith
in him as a leader?
I don't think that's it.
King Etoh has close ties
to the free knight Parn,
and he's also the High Priest
at the temple of Falis.
However, in times of war,
people seek out heroes.
No matter how skilled a
priest he is and no matter
how well he governs,
Etoh is not a warrior.
Not a warrior...
[LEAF]
Is this the royal palace?
[NEESE]
It's the holy palace.
We've come from the kingdom of
Flaim with an important dispatch
from King Kashue. I request
an audience with King Etoh.
We're glad you're here.
Some messengers from Flaim have
arrived! Lower the drawbridge!
[GARRACK grunting]
[LEAF] Garrack, you're so
jumpy. Is anything wrong?
Uh, no. I'm just a little
tense for some reason.
Perhaps you've got
a guilty conscious.
What? I haven't done
anything wrong, Leaf!
Then why are you so angry?
I'm not angry, so just shut up!
That's enough! Now quiet down!
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[GARRACK chuckles]
[SPARK growls]
[MESSENGER] I've brought the
messengers, Your Highness.
--[RYNA] Hmm?
--[NEESE giggles]
[door creaks]
Greetings, King Etoh.
From King Kashue of Flaim.
I welcome you to
the kingdom of Valis,
young messengers of Flaim.
Do you have something
you wish to give to me?
Yes!
The message is from King Kashue,
and I have read it.
Be sure to store this carefully.
Master Spark, are you aware
of what this message says?
Uh, no, sir. I'm not.
Is anything wrong?
Not as far as I can tell.
But King Kashue's message to me
also contained a
message for you.
But what did the message
say, Your Highness?
First, you must tell
me something, Spark.
Were you successful
in recovering
the stolen crystal ball?
Um... No, sir, we were not.
We were able to kill the
thieves, but they had already
handed off the treasure
to someone else.
How unfortunate.
[SPARK] Your Highness, I was
hoping that you would allow us
to continue our search
here in Valis.
No, I will not.
But... But why, sir?
The message says that if
you have not recovered
the Soul Crystal Ball by the
time you reach me, then you
and your entire party are to
return immediately to Flaim.
[gasping]
But, sir! Are you sure
that's what it said?!
[ALL gasping]
[gasps]
Forgive me!
That was very rude, sir.
[SPARK] How could I say that?!
King Etoh is a priest;
he wouldn't lie to me.
That was bad form.
Well? That is definitely what
King Kashue wrote, Master Spark.
[SPARK] And there goes
any chance I might've had
of completing my mission.
[SPARK groans]
[SPARK] Didn't King Kashue have
any hope for me at all...?
I bet he never expected me
to recover the crystal.
That's why he sent that message.
[RYNA]
King Kashue probably thought
it would be too
dangerous for you
to go searching through
Valis during war time.
She's right, Spark. The king
is concerned for your safety.
[SPARK] But--! If we don't
recover the Soul Crystal Ball,
well... then...
Then Neese will be--!
Spark, it's all right.
I'll be quite safe,
as long as the Staff
of Life remains
under close guard here in Valis.
Do you really believe it's safe?
Yes, I do.
Then so do I.
It's safe, but I can't stop
thinking about that ball.
I know... The bag man
has to come through Roid
to get the crystal to Kanon.
So, Captain, do we obey the
king's order and go home?
[SPARK]
Well, uh...
[RYNA] Or do we disobey and
continue on with our mission?
Hey, hey!
Excuse me, but I think I've
got an idea that might help.
We are all invited to
the banquet tonight
which gives us plenty
of time before sunset.
I suggest that we ask
to do a little sightseeing
by the waterfront.
That's nice. Then what?
Uh... Then we can investigate.
If we find a clue,
then we can think about
what we should do next.
Hey! You sorcerers are smart!
[ALDO] What do you think,
Priest Greevus?
While I don't think
it right to deceive,
I think even Myrii would forgive
the sin... in this case.
Well? That settles it!
Are you going to come
with us, Neese?
[NEESE] I'm sorry, but I must
spend some time with King Etoh.
I'll meet up with you later.
You may not know this,
but King Etoh
is an old friend
of Neese's family.
I see...
So... what now?
I think it's up to our captain.
Well then, Captain.
Come on! Captain!
[SPARK]
Uh...
Very well, then.
We've all worked too hard.
Let's do all that we can.
Okay, then! Let's go, everyone!
I'm not taking orders from you.
[LEAF]
Oh, shut up!
[SPARK] So, how can we
tell which of the ships
are suspicious and which aren't?
We're just going to
have to check each one.
But we can't be too
obvious about it,
or King Etoh will
find us out for sure.
[LEAF]
Come on, Captain.
Haven't you decided
what we're gonna do yet?
[sighs] I wish that Neese
was here to help us out.
[RYNA]
Hey, come on, now.
What are you all standing
around here for?
[SPARK]
It's Ryna.
At a time like this, we should
be mixing in with the crowds.
But what will we do then?
We spread a rumor that we're
looking for a ship to Kanon.
Then we can stand aside and let
our rumor find the ship for us.
I get you...
[LEAF]
Well, where do we go, Ryna?
How 'bout a place where there
are lots of sailors around?
[SPARK]
Hmm...
[gasps] Why, of course!
A tavern!
[RYNA]
Mm-hmm.
[slurps]
Excuse me, Leaf.
What is it?
Well, we didn't just come
here to eat, am I right?
[LEAF]
Absolutely! Why don't you start
spreading our rumor, Captain?
I'm eating as fast as I can.
[SPARK growls]
--[RYNA laughs]
---Huh?!
[SPARK]
Could you please not laugh?
Well, I guess it's
up to me, then.
[MEN chuckling]
[MAN A]
Gimme a li'l of that!
[RYNA]
Hey! That's not for you!
[MEN whooping]
How 'bout a drink, Barkeep.
Y-You wanna pay with this?
You can use what's left over
to buy a drink for everyone!
[MEN cheering]
Looks like business
has been good.
Well, there's a reason for that.
I'm looking for a ship
that's headed for Kanon.
If there is one,
I've got to get on it.
Don't you know that it's
against the law for anyone
to travel to Kanon while
we're at war with them?
If the guards ever find out,
they'll scoop you up.
[RYNA] I told you, I have
a reason. My friends and I
wanna become mercenaries
for the Marmo.
[BARKEEP]
Mercenaries for the Marmo?!
I-I won't know for sure without
asking the soldiers,
but... but...
But I can count on you, right?
Yeah...
Get me a name, and I'll
take care of you.
If you need me, I'll be
hanging around port.
And hurry up!
[BARKEEP]
Oh...
Okay. Now, let's move
on to the next one.
Uh... But shouldn't we
just wait here, Ryna?
The more we can spread
the word, Spark,
the better our chance of
finding someone. Am I right?
Yes, Ryna.
You're something else.
Really? You just
noticed that, huh?
[ETOH] You want to talk
about the Staff of Life,
don't you, Neese?
I do, Your Highness.
Nobody knows this, Neese,
but thieves broke into
the Temple of Falis as well.
[gasps]
Of course, the temple
soldiers drove them away
and the Staff of Life
is perfectly safe.
The god of Light shines his
protection on this place.
You are fortunate.
I am truly thankful
for His providence.
And what is going
to be the next step
on the journey of the Doorway?
Now that I know the
Staff of Life is safe,
I can travel on
with peace of mind.
[ETOH]
To Marmo?
[NEESE]
Mm. If I do nothing,
then the dark wizard
will surely snatch me up.
So I've decided to go there
and face things by myself.
And I want to recover the
Soul Crystal Ball as well.
As long as it remains
in Marmo hands,
Spark will never be
able to live it down.
I know how it feels
to want to help others,
but it's also important
for you to remember that
you're just one girl, Neese.
[NEESE]
Hmm?
It's impossible for
you to be all things.
It's okay for you to rely
on other people for help.
You may be right, but...
But now is the time
that I must be strong.
If I do not resist by myself,
then evil will take
over my heart!
I see you won't
change your mind.
[NEESE sighs]
May the god of Light shine his
glorious continence upon you.
I am grateful, King Etoh.
Thank you.
[RYNA]
Thanks.
Another miss.
That information we
got was all wrong.
[SPARK]
Dammit...
[GREEVUS]
Spark, it's sunset.
I'm afraid we have to
get back to the castle.
[SPARK groans]
I'm sorry I wasn't able to help.
Don't be. I'm sorry
I got you mixed up
in this in the first place.
Well, don't let
this get you down.
We did everything we could.
Let's take pride in that
and go back to Flaim.
Thank you. All of you.
[SAILOR A]
You there!
Are you the ones looking
for a ship to Kanon?
[SPARK]
Who are you?
[SAILOR B]
We don't have to tell you.
Great. We've got company.
We heard that you guys wanna
hook up with the Marmo.
[gasps]
Captain, I think
these guys are Marmo.
Yeah, that's right.
Then nobody move! Anyone who
associates with the Marmo
is an enemy of Valis!
We got trouble!
Who are these guys?!
[SPARK]
I-I think they're Valis sailors.
What do we do now? There's
no turning back, Captain!
[SPARK]
We can't fight our allies,
and we can't get arrested!
I say we run!
I'll use my magic on them.
[SPARK]
Go ahead, Aldo.
"Gentle airs that bring sleep,
manna of all creation.
Let your power permeate
their bodies and minds...
Let them feel the slumber
setting in..."
[gasping]
Now, go to sleep!
[ALL gasping]
Now's our chance!
Everybody, get out!
[SAILORS yelling]
[GREEVUS panting]
Wait, Garrack!
I'm right here.
[SPARK]
Garrack...
I know what you're
thinking, Captain.
You and I will hold
off these jokers
until the priest
gets away, right?
Let's give these guys a fight.
Make sure you don't slice me up.
I hear ya.
[GREEVUS]
Look out!
Forgive me, Priest Greevus!
[LEAF, RYNA giggle]
Uh... Thank you...
[SPARK]
Hyaa!
[GARRACK yells]
[GARRACK]
Damn!
Captain, I really think
it's time for us to go.
Yeah, but these guys
don't look like the type
who'll just let us.
[gasping]
[SAILOR C]
What the hell is that?!
[yelling]
[LEAF]
I summoned a will-o'-wisp.
[BOTH]
Huh?!
Now's your chance to get away!
I'll meet you there.
[SPARK panting]
[SPARK] I hope they all
make it back okay.
In here.
[GUARD E]
Stop him!
[SAILORS yelling]
[SPARK]
Damn!
[yelling continues]
[sighs]
That was close. Thanks a lot.
It's all right. You've got guts
taking on a bunch
of Valis sailors.
I didn't want to fight them.
[chuckles]
So what is your
next move gonna be?
You can stay if you wanna hide.
No! I've got to find my
friends. I'm going back.
You care about them.
That's good.
My name is Jay.
And if you feel like it, come by
the bridge with your friends
after the moon rises this night.
I'll take you to Kanon.
[gasps]
Then you can become
mercenaries for the Marmo.
[SPARK whimpers]
[snickers, laughs]
[SPARK, NEESE]
Welcome to Lodoss Island!
And now, what you've
all been waiting for,
the second part!
[LITTLE DRAGON]
Ah-ha!
[LITTLE DRAGON squeaking]
[SPARK]
Oh, I'm so beat...
I'm really glad that we're
finally out of that dungeon,
but why did we wander in
there in the first place?
It was the will of
the gods, you dope.
I guess you're right.
Hey, Neese...
You can use your magic to give
me my strength back, can't you?
Yeah...
I don't mean to impose, but...
Yeah? What the hey,
I'll give it a try.
That's great!
Lay it all me, mama!
"This is Neese calling Marfa,
mother of the Earth!"
Oh, I forgot.
How did it go again?
Oh, yeah, now I remember.
"Make it snappy,
don't take long.
Time to make this
weak guy strong!"
Whoa, mama!
[SPARK yells]
Oh, dear...
I think I screwed up.
[VOICE] Oh, ho, ho. What unusual
visitors you are there, huh?
It's a kindly priest.
I welcome you, and I want
to give you my, uh,
what-do-you-call-it,
kind thought of the day.
[NEESE]
Gee, thanks a lot!
And now, I'm going to tell
you my, uh, kind thought.
But before I do, I noticed you
have some yummy cookies there.
Do you think that I
could have one? Huh?
Back the hell off!
These cookies are reserved
for the mama dragon!
[LITTLE DRAGON squawking]
[PRIEST]
Whoa there! Ah!
[SPARK]
The Dark Elf!
Stifle yourself, cookie head!
He... vanished!
[DARK ELF] So, who's
the smart guy now, huh?
[DARK ELF]
Ouch.
This ain't over there, little
girl! Whoopty-doo, whoopty-doo!
This guy is such a lame villain.
You're tellin' me?
[NEESE, SPARK]
We'll be seeing you!
[NEESE] We meet a mysterious
man in the port of Roid.
From what he tells us, we
believe that the holy kingdom
is about to be attacked.
Are they aiming for the Staff
of Life at the temple of Falis?
What will Spark decide to do?
Next time, on
Record of Lodoss War :
Chronicles of the
Heroic Knight :
"Decision...
An Option Compelled."