Well, it's Gin Tama's
six month anniversary
since the show started!
Yeah, although for a while,
I was like
"Damn they're totally
gonna cancel our show."
We made it by the skin
of our teeth.
Yeah, but, no one
expected us to last,
so apparently nobody
prepared anything at all
for the upcoming episodes.
Whatever, it doesn't matter.
They can just make one of those clip
show episodes to fill the gaps.
We can fool everyone
as long as we are sure
to insert two or three
new clips into the episode.
Hey!
Well then, why don't we go down
memory lane with the past episodes?
We've sure been through a lot,
haven't we?
Like Shinpachi getting
stuck in that ditch,
and Shinpachi puking in his sleep,
and Shinpachi puking in his sleep...
Hey!
That's such a lie!
And why are you mentioning
puking twice?
Enough puking!
That's the idea, Shinpachi, recap
everything that's happened until now.
No thank you.
Real men don't dwell on the past.
You're beginning to talk big for a
Shinpachi!
I guess a person changes
if you give them six months.
Oh yes, they change.
In six months, this little weakling
has turned into a macho lover boy.
That's not true, Kagura!
Absolutely not true!
Order now and get an extra can
of protein powder free of charge!
No thanks!
I still have some cans at home.
You actually ordered some?
I was a naive and unsuspecting child.
A jug of snake oil works better
than those silly workout products.
Those don't work!
You're being fooled!
She means using the jugs as
weights for your workouts.
Is your name Jackie Chan?
And besides, Jackie's already a grandpa!
Oh man, when did I stop
going to see his movies?
Jackie Chan movies are like the turning
point of when a boy turns into a man.
That's a disputable line of division.
Hey, listen, those who belittle
Jackie will pay for his sins!
I will not!
Try jumping off a watchtower
or onto a chandelier!
I wouldn't even if I could!
And why are you so hooked
on Jackie Chan today?
Are you a resident of
Jackie Village or something?
Alright, has it been five minutes, yet?
Nope, only one minute and
fifty seconds.
There's still lots more time.
Don't you think...
maybe if we keep doing this,
the producers will get angry at us?
The producers?
Like who?
Well, I mean like...
Someone watching this
or being shown this...
or being made to listen to this.
People like that.
Man, what a pain.
I guess we have no choice,
let's start it up!
Hey, what's this?
Are we still on this cut?
Let's start then.
The "Gin Tama celebrating
six month anniversary" Special!
The "This happened,
that happened,
all the things that happened"
highlight special!
Enjoy!
Hey, guys, this is supposed
to be a highlight special.
We're supposed to be looking back.
Somebody look back, would you?
Nope. Somebody needs
to watch the pot, you know.
So I'll watch it, and you two can
look back all you want, okay?
No way, I'll watch the pot,
Shinpachi, just start us off.
You were made for this kind of thing!
Have some confidence in yourself.
I really don't like backhanded
compliments like that.
Kagura, why don't you go, huh?
No way!
I know you guys are gonna try to eat
all the beef while I look away.
Sheesh, why don't you give us a
freaking break, Kagura, will you?
You really think we'd do
something that desperate?
Hah.
This is supposed
to be a happy occasion.
Could you not say such
hurtful things right now?
Sure, we practically never ever
get to eat hotpots.
But this is a special occasion...
and we're here to celebrate
all of us together,
and you really had to say such
an awful thing at a time like this?
This is awful.
Yeah, I can say that this is really
depressing me, Kagura.
That was a pretty mean thing to say,
Kagura.
You should apologize.
Mmmmm...
Okay, damn it.
I'm sorry for being such a hobo.
This is our chance!
Go now!
Oh man, it looks like the precious
beef has totally disintegrated.
Look at that.
You guys pulled on it way too hard.
Don't you think you're a bit
too excited over just a hotpot?
Damn it, you guys!
You both tricked me!
Honestly, I'm starting to
lose faith in humanity,
and it's all because of you guys!
That's how people grow up
to become adults, Kagura.
Good for you kiddo!
You're one step closer
to becoming an adult.
Besides, didn't I teach you that the
dinner table is a battlefield?
Have you forgotten that already?
I'll never believe anything
Gin says ever again!
You're all my enemies!
I won't trust anyone ever again.
Yes, that's a good mentality to have.
Hate me more.
Detest me!
And despise me!
Use the power of that hatred
and let it flow through you,
to make it through this
rotten world we live in.
The only thing rotten in this world
is your head!
This is bad.
It's just as I feared.
Having a hotpot dinner
here at Odd Jobs right now,
is like throwing Noel Marshall
into a den of lions.
At this rate, all the beef
will be torn into shreds
before it even hits our tongues.
Rather than thinking about how to
eat more beef then anyone else,
I should be thinking about
protecting it from those greedy two.
But they're like a bunch
of feral cats right now.
If I end up provoking them,
it'll backfire.
No.
They're both stupid,
but their pride is first class.
So if I target that.
It's a huge risk, but this is the
only way to protect the beef!
You guuys, I think I'm out.
I don't want to eat this if we
have to fight over it.
This is just pathetic.
I actually had barbeque
with my sister yesterday.
I'm kind of sick of beef...
especially since I can
have it anytime I want.
You two can continue to go at it.
I mean, if you guys still really want it.
Come!
Come on!
Bring it on!
Oh, well then.
It's not like I really wanted
to eat beef today,
we just happened to come
into some money.
So I thought we'd splurge and
have a hot pot for dinner,
but if it's gonna be like this
I guess we'll have to call it quits.
You guys really alright with that?
Yeah, that's totally fine with me!
I'm not particularly eager to eat
beef for dinner, either.
I'm a vegetarian, after all!
Let's just stop this crap then,
forget the hotpot!
I can't be bothered
with this, damn it!
Yes!
But I think my act was more
effective than I anticipated.
It feels like this might just
end right here.
Damn it.
I'm the one that started
saying such a thing,
so I can't backtrack and suggest
we heat up the pot again.
And besides...
it would be embarrassing.
This is bad.
I wanted to neutralize
the situation,
so I followed along
with Shinpachi...
but I didn't expect
Kagura to agree.
It's going to take a miracle
to start up the hotpot dinner
again in this situation.
However, if I don't do anything,
there won't be a
hotpot dinner for sure.
And we haven't
even gotten started.
No way!
I must avoid that at all costs.
Someone, make a move.
I want to eat beef.
I'm craving it so badly.
I want to stuff myself with it!
Come on, Shinpachi!
Say something.
Please!
I'll even give you 2 bucks, Shinpachi!
Come on, someone!
Say something!
I want to eat beef!
I haven't actually eaten any beef
for nearly six months!
We're all the same!
We're all one at heart,
aren't we? Aren't we?
‐Huh?
What?
What's that?
Hey, Kagura, what's up?
You aren't hungry, are you?
No, I'm not hungry.
That was a fart.
No way, that wasn't a fart.
That was your stomach growling.
I'm sure of it.
So what?
Are you that hungry or what?
I'm not hungry at all.
I'm feeling full.
Look, I think if you're really that
hungry, let's all have some hotpot?
It doesn't matter to me,
but what do you wanna do?
I'm okay either way, but Kagura...
you don't need to hold back
if you're hungry.
That's right.
I honestly don't care either way...
but it's right in front of us.
Yeah, I don't care either way,
but it would be wasteful to leave it,
as far as I'm concerned.
I'm hungry, but it's okay.
I have my pickled seaweed.
‐You idiot!
What did you think was going to happen
when a growing child keeps eating
junk like that without
eating proper food?
Do you not have
any sympathy}
for all of the farmers and all of the cows?
Hm?
C'mon.
I'll serve you some of it.
You sure?
I'm sure.
I said I bought it for
you guys didn't I?
Hurry and eat kid, or I will kill you!
Oh well, then I guess
we'll eat too, all right?
Not that I'm especially hungry.
What a bother.
But if I don't join you,
I'll spoil the mood.
Shinpachi, you ready to eat?
Oh, okay.
Not that I'm craving beef
much either.
But I've been taught that it's
wasteful to leave food uneaten.
I'm vigilant when it comes
to things like this.
Phew...
got past that hurdle.
But it's definitely going
to be much harder
than before to reach for some beef.
After refusing the hot pot already...
there's an undeniable air of
hesitation among us now.
Come on, isn't there something
to break this tension?
Isn't there...
something?
‐Isn't there...
‐something?!
Elizabeth, that was a very close call.
What're you guys doing here?!
We ran into some
unforeseen circumstances.
Oh yeah?
Is that right?
Big liar!
Egg‐scuse me,
but I'm going to need you to lettuce
hide here for a beef moment.
Then I promise we'll
be onion our way.
What is this person saying?!
At it again, eh, Cobra?
My name is Katsura, not Cobra.
It's so obvious his story
is a big fat lie!
But his entrance has blown
the situation out of the water.
Even if we question his motives..
Oh look, you figured me out?
He's prepared to charm his way out.
I've gotta get him out of here.
He's definitely thought this through.
Oh please, oh please.
Let's all enjoy this
delicious food together.
Wh‐What's that?
What is this pretty boy thinking?
Trying to act all nice
and sweet, is he?
Sweeter than eating pop tarts
with apple sauce.
Hey, that sounds really good.
I think I'll try it next time.
But more importantly...!
Thank you so much.
The aura of hesitation
that our war of words
created has dissipated
thanks to their entrance.
So now.
The challenge is who
will go on the offensive
in this quiet calm and grab the
first piece of beef for himself!
The one prepared to own up
to the titles, "petty and greedy"...
and the one who is able
to take the first bite...
regardless of the others before him,
will have the right to control the
pot and all the beef inside it.
And the right to the title of.
‐The Hotpot Shogun!
Well, here goes the first strategy!
The one who takes command wins!
At this point...
the one closest to being the
Hotpot Shogun is Kagura, of course.
Although she hasn't actually
touched the pot yet.
But once she finishes eating
what's in her bowl,
she has the power right now
to reach for her next serving.
However, there's no need
to worry about her.
From her face, it's obvious that she's
relishing the taste of the vegetables.
Among girls her age...
there are many fools who think
that eating vegetables
is way cooler than eating
high‐caloric meat.
And these other two.
They're not too dangerous.
That's because both of
them are here as guests.
In their position, the chance that they'll
make a move for the pot first is zero.
After urging them several times,
they might finally take
some cabbage or
something unimportant to eat.
Nope, one can't underestimate Cobra.
My name is Katsura, not Cobra.
There's a very high possibility that he'll
ignore this high‐charged atmosphere
and go right into the pot
with his chopsticks.
I guess we can ignore
that weird‐looking beast.
No way can he use chopsticks
with those hands.
Holy crap!
He is dexterous!
The biggest problem is still
with Shinpachi, though.
He quickly figured out a young girl's
tastes and preferences,
and subtly plated a huge
serving of vegetable for her.
No doubt, that guy is shrewd.
Darn it!
Why didn't I offer a bowl of
vegetables to Gin after Kagura?
I take on the role of
the generous friend,
and then take a serving
last for myself.
And in the process, if I had changed
the layout of the food in the pot,
or given myself the opportunity to
reach into the pot more often...
the title of the Hotpot Shogun
would have been mine!
Wait!
Kagura is almost done eating.
How about if I offer to
fill her bowl again?
No, damn it!
I won't have a second chance.
That's because she's sure to
want to do it herself this time.
She won't take kindly
to someone's offer.
Well then, this is all or nothing!
So, then, don't you guys think.
They say "Friendship,
persistence, victory..."
Kids these days know how
short‐lived friendship can be,
as well as the futility of victory.
So all you need is to be
a massive genius.
Got it!
Hey, isn't the heat too low
on this thing?
The Hotpot Shogun...
is me!
Huh?
Chopsticks?
No way!
In that split second?
And Goooo!
Chopstick Scud Missile!
Heh...
Huh?
All these days of obscurity
were for this moment!
Damn, my sides were exposed.
Curse you, Cobra!
My name is Katsura not Cobra.
Oh sorry, I think I might
have caught a cold.
Huh?!
What was that?
She didn't use her hands or her
chopsticks, but with one sneeze.
She decided the outcome
in one move?
This strategy.
Well frankly, I don't feel like
eating a hotpot like that.
She's the only one who'll
eat the hotpot now.
Are you saying she won through
her innocence and purity?
No...
this girl!!
The title of Hotpot Shogun is mine!
She's not pure at all!
This kid has vegetable
coming out of her nose!
Kagura, what a frightening child!
Did you just realize it,
little boys?
From the moment when
I made my stomach growl,
to the moment I was concentrating
on eating my bowl of vegetables.
It was all an act,
a mere ruse to put all
of you greenhorns off guard...
and take the seat of
the Hotpot Shogun.
Well, you can suck it up and
watch as this little girl terrorizes
all of your beloved beef!
No way!
She's swallowing it in one gulp!
People of the Yato Clan must have
monstrous bellies!
Good evening!
Say, what's all this?
Don't tell me you've
all started already?
Did you forget about us?
I thought I told you to wait
until we got here
before you started cooking.
As if any of these guys know
what patience is, Ms. Otose.
Too bad, old biddies.
The beef you came to eat is all...
Hey, what's this meat
you've been using?
Don't tell me you're having
pork in your hotpot?
Come on!
Isn't this a party?
How pitiful.
Pork is just perfect
for these guys.
Pork?
Th‐That's ridiculous!
Impossible!
It definitely tasted like beef.
The flavor of beef...
like a cheese burger,
breakfast cheese burger,
and double bacon cheese burger,
the kind I eat sometimes.
She's right!
It was the same scent as that
aroma that wafts through the air
for a brief moment when I
walk by that burger shop.
Well, I've never actually had any before,
but I know it was beef!
Move aside.
This is my seat, of course.
Geez, fine.
No way!
Yes, way!
All that meat you've been eating,
believing it to be beef, was actually...
‐Cheap cuts of pork!
Did you really think an
expensive delicacy...
a food like beef would really be
sitting on our tables, little girl?
As if I'd share it even if I had some.
Th‐That's not...
So everything
I believed was a lie.
All characters appearing are fictious,
and any resemblance
to real persons,
living or dead,
is purely coincidental?
At that moment.
I felt an insecurity, like my legs
were crumbling underneath me.
I won't trust anyone anymore,
I can't trust anyone!
Oh Pork, oh Pork!
Wherefore art thou Pork?
I really hope you all break
the bone in your little toe!
Victory.
One down.
Cobra is sure tough to take down.
My name is Katsura, not Cobra.
And as if I'd die over
a wound like this!
I still haven't accomplished
anything in life!
You gotta eat something good
at least once in a while.
I splurged a little bit and I've got
the expensive cuts today.
And now let's eat some good food,
drink some good drinks,
and celebrate with a
good meal!
Oh! Mt. Fuji!
Geisha!
Oh, wasabi!
All right, it's almost ready to eat.
This is it.
An old hag with one foot
in the grave...
and a middle‐aged broad
with one foot in the mud.
A man who's middle name
is "flat broke,"
and an organism who's
middle name is a "mystery."
‐Easy foes!
He's the problem.
Hey, Gin, let's settle this like men.
Otose, may I serve you?
I made the first move!
That guy!
He's using the same strategy!
This time, I'll become the
Hotpot shogun for sure!
Oh, don't you worry about us.
Let's just all serve ourselves.
Shucks!
I didn't see that coming!
Now everyone will indiscriminately reach
into the hotpot for all the good stuff!
Heh, it backfired.
He was so caught up in his
thoughtfulness strategy.
That he was blind to the possibility
of a counter to it!
You can blame your
own youth for that!
It is true, I admit I failed, sure.
But I won't concede defeat just yet!
That's true.
No need to overthink this anymore.
I agree.
Real men don't turn their
backs when there's a fight.
Considering the amount
of time we have left,
we have no other option but
to go all in once right now!
The one who reaches
the pot first wins!
‐The Hotpot Shogun...
‐is me!
is me!
Wh‐what?
What's that?
What is it?
R‐Ridiculous!
How could this...?
Forget the beef...
I can't even get close...
to the pot!
However, there's no way...
‐we will lose!
They're beyond the realm
of Hotpot Shogun.
‐They are.
‐Hotpot.
Emperors!
Th‐They're just in a different
class from us!
The pot is so far.
I can't reach it!
Why'd they even come here?Just to torment us?
What were we fighting for until now?
We were like frogs in a well,
fighting and hurting each other.
Was all that suffering meaningless?
‐No...!
‐What's this?
‐What's all this?
And this is why...!
We can't let our fighting be in vain!
This is why, we can't...
‐lose this battle!
Absultely no way!
Go, Kagura!
You must become...
‐Napotleon!
It smells kind of sour and
it doesn't taste that good.
I think I prefer pork.
Why you!
Are you screwing with us?
‐Seriously?
‐Spit it out!
‐Spit it all out, Kagura!
‐Oh my goodness...
Humans are so worthless.
Tucker?
You're Tucker, my classmate
from school, aren't you?
Why'd you end up joining
a bike gang?
If only...
If only I had rescued
you back then!
The next episode...