I hooked one, this time
it's really a big one.
You're not getting away.
What the hell is this?
Ever since the Sky People came
the Earth's ecosystem
has gotten really weird.
Whatever, man,
just put it in the bucket.
What?
‐We're really eating this?
‐Of course we're eating it!
Sea cucumber and
Natto tastes good, right?
The more grotesque it looks,
the better it tastes when you eat it...
Even ugly women always have at
least one or two good points.
Hey, Gin, Gin!
Look here, I really caught a huge one!
Look, look!
It doesn't really hurt?
No, it does hurt!
No!
Hey, Gin, can we eat
this one too?
No!
Our dinner!
Now forget everything
you just saw, got it?
Gintoki, was that a
swamp monster, a Kappa?
As if such a thing exists!
It was just, you know, a regular old bald
dude who lives in the pond.
"Regular old bald dudes"
don't live in ponds, Gin.
And besides, he was kinda green.
That's because...
Oh, you know...
He's got some drinking problems.
Everyone would stop
drinking if it made them
look like a low budget grinch!
You bastards!
My glasses are broken, damn it!
Call your parents!
You guys are gonna
buy me a new pair!
It's alive!
Hey!
Come back here, you guys!
You're not getting away!
I want your names
and addresses!
If you had apologized
at the start,
I wouldn't be so angry
with you about this.
If you do something wrong, the
right thing to do is to apologize.
Why did you run?
Um, well, because you're a kappa.
A kappa?
What is that?
Don't try to trick me by talking
such nonsense!
You're the one that's
making no sense, dude!
What is it about me that doesn't
make any sense, girl?
And my name isn't dude,
its Mr. Ebina.
We're sorry, Mr.Ebina.
Uh, I'll break my glasses, too,
so please forgive us.
That was a very fine apology, son.
Why don't you take this biscuit
as a reward?
Thanks but no thanks,
I'll pass on that.
Well, it's a good thing it was
only my glasses that broke.
If it was the dish on my head that broke,
this old man would have lost it.
I'd have beaten you all to a pulp, huh?
Listen up.
This dish is like a vital organ.
My life actually depends on this thing.
‐No!
‐The dish on his head broke!
Oh man!
The dish on his head broke!
Though I don't know whats
so bad about that!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I was practicing my golf swing
and the club...
it just slipped out of my hands!
This is why I told you you
should leave this place.
This isn't your home.
This is my property.
I bought out this entire area.
You should shut up!
I've been living here since before you
even came out of your
father's ball sack!
Why should I be the
one to leave here?
And stop staring at me!
It's embarrassing!
No cameras please.
Seriously...
He just got a bit shy
after his dish cracked.
I thought his life depended
on that thing.
I am planning to build a huge
golf course on this land,
and this pond just happens
to be in the way!
I'll find you another pond
for you to settle into,
so would you please
just leave nicely?
That's not the issue here at all!
This pond doesn't belong only to me.
It also belongs to...
I don't really understand
what you're saying,
but if you're going to
cause me any more trouble,
you'd better be prepared
for what's coming.
You'd better keep an eye out for any
stray golf balls coming your way!
There, now it's fixed, old man.
Did I just hear a
cracking noise rigth now?
It's just your imagination.
Say old man, if you're going
to move, we can help you.
It's none of your business, moptop!
Look over there.
See that odd‐looking island?
That's the spaceship I rode
here on a long time ago.
Mr. Ebina, you're an Amanto, then?
My species cannot survive
without any clean water.
A long time ago,
our planet lost all its water in a
catastrophic natural disaster.
So we set out to find
a brand new home.
I found my way to this planet
full of water.
Planet Earth...
I was amazed to find out such
a lovely planet could exist.
At the time, there were
hardly any Amanto,
so I felt as though I had
this jewel all to myself.
But the people of the Earth
only saw me
as nothing more than a monster.
I was persecuted and forced to return
to this pond to live in solitude.
But you know,
you can only truly feel alive when
you have other people around
you to connect with.
Sure I found a safe place to live,
but I may as well have been dead.
Until...
I met her, that is.
She appeared one day
along the pond bank.
She didn't do anything,
she would just always
stare out at the water.
At first, I hid from her, but...
after a while it just seemed silly...
You there, why do you
always just sit there?
The girl looked at me,
and was a bit surprised, but...
It's boring being all alone
in my bedroom,
so I thought "why not be
alone out here?"
But I guess there
were two of us.
The girl had
tuberculosis,
very contagious.
She had been sneaking out of her
room where she was kept isolated
because no one wanted
to be around her.
She didn't care who I was,
she just wanted
someone to talk to.
That was exactly what I wanted.
Ever since then, the only
time I really felt alive...
was when I was talking with her.
We only ever talked about silly things,
but it was fun.
You're very lucky, mister.
How so?
You can swim freely in such
lovely water as this.
I've been very frail since
I was a tiny child...
so I've never been
able to swim at all.
I wish I could swim
like you, just once.
In that translucent world.
Just strengthen your body then.
That's impossible.
I've been like this all my life.
Oh,silly girl!
Life is very long.
I'll protect this place until you're
strong and healthy.
I'll keep it
just as beautiful as it is now.
So, all you need to do
is hurry and get well.
All right, then.
It's a promise, mister Pinky swear.
You bet!
A pinky swear promise?
How many decades ago was that?
Who knows?
But then...
the ship he came on looks like
it's been there a long time.
So its likely that that girl is already...
This guy is way too die hard.
I can't go along with this.
Okay!
Everything good?
Right, get to it.
Right.
I've just about had it with
that rotten kappa out there,
so I'm going to fill this
entire lake with dirt.
But are you sure it's okay?
What about the kappa's curse?
You idiot!
There's no such thing
as a real kappa!
That's just an Amanto
in the water.
Damn it man.
Why do we have to do this
in the middle of the night?
What's going on?
It stopped!
Hi, I am Kappa number three.
Got a cucumber, mister?
What's going on with Nojima?
Hey, what's going on?
Did you get your balls caught
in the bulldozer or something?
It is me, Kappa Number Two!
What's with all that screaming
over there?
Did you get your balls caught
in the bulldozer or something?
Onishi!
Go take a look at, huh?
Onishi?
Who are you?
We are the tree Kappa brothers
from Lake Toya.
I am the eldest of the three kappa
brothers, Kappa Number One.
I would leave this property
alone if I were you,
or you'll feel the wrath
of the kappa's curse!
No, no, please.
Please!
What do kappas want?
Cucumbers, right?
Tell me what you want!
I don't have much hair,
but I have plenty of money, of course!
What we like?
Let's see...
We like sweets, I guess.
And guys who are a bit too die hard.
Hey, there.
You're here again?
Hey, I heard the news.
Seems this land was
put up for sale...
Sounds like you'll be okay
for a little while.
Yeah, apparently some real
kappa appeared here.
Now that would be pretty scary.
Could it have been you?
Hey!
I didn't know there were such
beautiful fish living in this pond.
It sure seems to be having
a good time!
Four hundred and sixty two.
What's that number?
The number of people who
have collapsed this summer
from heatstroke so far.
Are you serious?
Gin, can we just buy an
air conditioner already?
This year's heat wave is too much
to get by with just a simple fan.
Don't be ridiculous.
Where are we going to
find the money for that?
Forget about conditioning our air
learn to condition your mind.
Suppress your mind to a state of
nothingness and even...
the South Pole can be as
cold as the North Pole.
Gin, just so you know they
call it the "south" pole,
but that doesn't mean
it's always summer there.
I already knew that.
I know the South Pole isn't
an endless summer paradise,
but what I'm trying to say...
is that if you suppress your mind
to a state of nothingness...
Actually, it doesn't do anything.
Shame on you!
I think your brain's turned
into burnt toast.
This is totally ridiculous.
What was the point of
this conversation?
First of all, try going out
on a day like this.
You'll collapse before you can
buy an air conditioner.
The best thing to do
on a day like this is
to lay around the house
and do nothing.
So it would seem that the
fan is our only lifeline.
I think we should all be
careful not to break it.
I just can't stand it!
What's hot is hot even if
I suppress my mind.
Why do I have to go outside and
buy a fan on a day like this?
What a pain in the ass!
Maybe I'll just buy an air
conditioner instead.
What do you say, old man?
Should I upgrade to
an air conditioner?
Well, I don't see why not.
You don't see why not?
Where am I going to find the money
to buy an air conditioner?
Mind your own business!
Why do I have to get drenched in
sweat to go and buy a machine
that makes me cooler?
It's like digging for buried
gold with buried gold.
Like drinking before drinking.
When the next fan arrives,
I'm going to bully him.
For three days and three nights,
I'm going to let it
blow out the window.
Man this really ticks me off.
Maybe I'll just buy an air conditioner!
But I don't have any money.
An electric fan?
I'm sorry, sir, but we don't
have anything like that here.
These days, everyone uses air
conditioners, you know?
How about it, mister?
Why not use this opportunity
to make an upgrade?
‐I'll make it cheap.
‐You mean that?
Okay, then, sir.
What do you say, then,
to 10 bucks?
Step right up!
Come one, come all!
‐Mister? That's very strange.
‐You don't make any eye contact with me anymore.
An electric fan?
No, no, no.
Maybe you should try
an antique shop.
A fan?
You're using a fan
in this day and age?
Isn't that like so crazy?
That's like so retro!
That's like so crazy retro!
A fa...?
What're you doing?
I haven't said anything yet!
Put me down! Put me down!
‐Put me down.
‐Shut up!
You probably don't
have one anyway.
I already know that.
‐I already did some research
‐Put me down! Put me down!
at the back alley shops, and nothing!
Grrr, this is really pissing me off!
Even that beautiful
blue sky ticks me off!
And it's so blue!
Why am I soaking with sweat and
passing around from store to store
just to buy a measly fan?
Hey, there, mister,
can I go home now?
Can I just go home already?
Well, I don't see why you couldn't.
You don't see why I couldn't?
I've already been through
hell itself for this!
You don't know a thing at all!
Don't act like you do!
Damn it.
This is wrong, this is so wrong.
I'm here to buy a fan.
I came all this way to cool down!
But I'm just getting more
and more heated!
This seriously ticking me off!
I should've just gotten
an air conditioner!
But I don't have any money.
My, my. It's unusual to have a
samurai for a customer here.
Welcome.
An electric fan...
You have an electric fan, don't you?
Go get me one!
A fan.
How nostalgic, isn't it?
Tell me, where did you hear
about such a rare thing?
It doesn't matter, just go get one!
Now hold on just a moment.
You're the first person
who's come this far for one.
At least tell me your name.
What do you need
my name for, lady?
I'm just a customer.
Customer?
That's a very fine name then.
I'll be seeing you, then, Customer!
Whoa!
What'd you do
that for, you freak!
Manager!
Where's the manager?
Let go of me!
I'll never let an evil syndicate like
yours have the fan, I swear it!
What kind of nonsense
are you talking about?
Calm down.
Are you're mistaking me for
someone else, is that it?
I just came to buy a fan.
Hey!
What's the matter?
Blood?
What?
Manager!
Where's the manager?
I have found it at last.
The sewer rat's nest.
We didn't think anyone other
than that woman survived.
But it seems that your luck
has just run out.
Earth Defense Army.
What?
Are you talking to me?
Earth Defen...
Say what?
Don't play dumb, you scumbag!
I know that you're a remnant
of the Earth Defense Army!
Earth Defense Army?
I did once build a bookshelf
from milk cartons
‐to protect the environment, but an army.
‐Don't give me that!
Hand over the fan right now!
Oh, so then you're here to
buy an electric fan, too?
Is there a retro fad going
on or something?
I didn't know they were
that popular these days.
No wonder I can't buy one.
I'm not letting...
anyone have the fan.
You'll never get is
as long as I live!
This is... a grena...
Why does this
always have to
happen to me?
All I wanted was to buy a fan.
I don't even know who you are,
but you don't seem
to be a bad person.
I already told you,
I just came here to buy a fan.
But I'd rather give it to you than
hand it over to those guys.
Will you take care of this for me?
Hey, are you listening?
I said I only came here to buy a fan.
The fan is sealed at that location.
I want you to go there,
and destroy the
fan for me.
You're telling someone who came
to buy a fan to go destroy it?
It's an evil machine that
destroys human souls.
It's not something people
should be allowed to have.
What do you mean?
Are you talking about
how you get your hands
caught if you stick it in?
That does hurt.
Everyone does that
at least once.
My father was one of the top
mechanical engineers in Edo City.
People sought his skills and
made my father build that thing.
But it was the last machine
that my father ever built.
I managed to retrieve
the fan from those men,
but I haven't had the heart to
destroy it.
This is all because I was too weak.
But if that falls into their
hands, it's all over.
Please just take the fan and...
Hurry up and go!
But I just...
Save this city,
I'm begging you to
save the Earth!
I keep telling you, I just came
here to buy a simple fan!
Something's wrong.
Something's very wrong!
I came to buy a simple fan!
Tell me, why is this
happening to me?
‐Stop rigth there!
‐Hey, old man!
Why is this happening to me?!
What's going on?
Just Tell me!
I'm sorry, I don't know.
I don't know, either, Moron!
Go to hell!
I have come way too
far to turn back now!
The fan...
is mine!
What?
Who the hell is that guy?
Was there such a monster
in the Earth Defense Army?
After him!
Don't let him get away!
We must retrieve
the fan at any cost!
What is this place?
There's nothing but junk in here.
Where's the fan.
Where's the fan, is it in here?
What is this?
This huge storefront cat
seriously gives me the creeps.
Up we go.
And.
back, back, back down!
Are these...
gold coins?
Surprised, are you?
That's the robotic gold‐coin
counterfeiting machine no.3
built by the brilliant mechanical
engineering prodigy.
In other words,
thid s a fake money maker,
which is all ready to use,
and is now in full throttle
kind of machine.
We call it the FAN, for short!
Thank you for showing us
the way to get in here.
Now hand over the FAN!
You'll do it if you value her life!
Don't worry about me at all!
Just destroy it like I told you!
Where's the spinning part?
‐What?
‐I mean, not this.
but the part that whirls
around and blows air.
I'm asking you where that is!
No!
What have you done?
The FAN!
Do you have any idea
what that's worth,
and you destroyed it?
Giving it such a confusing name!
I'll phone the consumer advocates
on you bastards.
I'm soaking with sweat.
I've had to work so hard.
and even trashed my mo‐ped.
Curse you, you Damned
Earth Defense Army!
You won't get away with this!
Now that it's come to this,
I'll use my greatest secret weapon
to put an end to you.
This stupid thing.
I should've just bought
an air conditioner.
Air conditioners are the
way of the future.
Oh yeah, I don't have any money.
Now die!
What?
You...
stupid bastard!
Wait a second!
Thank you so much.
You're the hero
who saved Edo City.
Please let me repay you.
I don't have much, but I do
have an air conditioner at home.
I don't want an air conditioner.
I already told you like I said
from the beginning, I...
So now you understand it.
Took blood, sweat and more sweat
to get this fan here.
And look.
Just look at its brilliant luster
that this thing has.
Doesn't that look a little bit filthy?
That's because your eyes are
a little bit filthy, Shinpachi.
Now this time, use it carefully
so you don't break it.
Hold on, you were the
one who broke it.
What's this?
That's odd.
It won't turn on.
You cheapskate!
I'll bet you picked
that up from the dump,
and made up that whole
story to cover it.
What the hell is the
Earth Defense Army?
Your story was way too long!
You big liar!
You big, fat liar!
What did you use the money
you took with for?
‐Gambling?!
‐Wait a minute!
It really is the truth!
I destroyed an evil organization!
Listen, I really did save
the world, it's the truth!
Stop going to the
Cabaret club so often!