Happy New Year...
and please keep watching
the show!
Whoa!
What happened?
The sky is all white...
I'm the one all white, but why....
Why am I sleeping...
in a strange place like this?
Has something like this
happened before?
We might be having...
abnormal weather this winter or
something...
But when raindrops fall...
you wash yourself
in an outdoor tub!
And when spears fall,
you'd do a bamboo dance,
you have fun no matter
what the situation...
That's the Edo spirit!
On that note...
let the First Wacky Kabukicho
Snow Festival begin!
Look, Gin!
I brought you some snow.
Oh, leave it right there.
Wow, everyone is making
great sculptures.
They're all pretty naughty looking,
though.
I guess that's Kabukicho, for you...
As for the Odd Jobs team,
we are...
Well, this looks very good...
Now I just have to erect
the rod in between them...
Whoa!
Our show is gonna
end right now!
Hey, hey...
what are you doing, huh?
I can't believe you just did that?
Do you know how hard I worked
to make that left ball?
Speak for yourself!
Don't you know how much
trouble the producer
will have to go through if
you do something like that?
Hey, Gin, I finished the rod.
What are you holding,
Kagura, oh no?!
Shinpachi, what's the big fuss?
I don't know what you think
this is, but look...
we are building...
the Neo Armstrong Cyclone
Jet Armstrong Cannon.
You said Armstrong twice!
There's no way such an
erotic cannon exists!
Damn teenagers!
They're mind is filled
with dirty thoughts...
Whenever you hear "rod" or
"balls" you immediately assume
we're talking about something dirty.
Yeah, you're really disgusting.
Don't talk to me for a while, okay?
Then, what is it, huh?
Oh, what do you know?
You guys are here, too?
Oh, Hasegawa.
Please stop these guys.
Those two are making
something filthy...
Hey, isn't that...
a Neo Armstrong Cyclone
Jet Armstrong Cannon?
Wow, it looks so authentic!
How do you know what that is?!
Does it really exist?
Seriously? Am I the only one
who doesn't know anything?!
It was the Dog Star System's
ultimate weapon.
They used it to blow up Edo Castle Tower
and force Japan to surrender.
What?
Our country lost because of
this stupid looking cannon?
So, Hasegawa,
what are you doing here?
Well, I've created my own
sculpture for the contest...
I heard the winner gets
a big cash prize.
Wow!
It looks so amazing.
I have no idea what it is,
but it looks amazing!
Well, yeah...
it's nothing really.
I tend to put in a lot of effort when
making something, so I couldn't stop...
I call it "Flight."
Wow, it's really fantastic!
Are you the model for this,
Hasegawa?
Huh, Well, I put my heart
and soul into it,
so it ended up looking like me.
This statue is too muscular
to be you.
Let me scrape some
off around here.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Give me a break!
This thing's actually really
delicately balanced!
Oh?
So then it even
resembles your life.
I wonder if that part looks
like dork's too.
No! Stop pointing your finger at that!
Hey, hey, don't show our
Kagura a dirty thing like that!!
Hold on!
You see things like this in
museums all the time!
I mean, it's not dirty, it's art!
Bastard!
Are you trying to get this
show cancelled?
Hey!
Watch where you're throwing
that snowball!
Hey!
Take that!
Whoa!
My Dandy Outstanding Refined Knob.
In short, my Dork!
‐It got stuck!
Hey!
How could you stick that dirty
thing onto our masterpiece?!
They're coming!
Do something, Shinpachi!
This is really great work.
Oh, really?
Hey, you guys!
You two are really so mean!
I bet you did that on purpose.
No, I didn't mean it.
But if we left it as it was,
I'm sure
we would have got angry
calls from the PTA.
That thing you're making is
barely safe, you know.
Hey, I just came up
with a great idea.
Let's add some wings.
Some wings.
Yeah, Gin, that sounds great!
How did you come up
with such a great idea?
Well, I don't know, but it
suddenly just came to me.
Oh?
You guys are here, too?
Katsura.
I suppose this is the Neo Armstrong
Cyclone Jet Armstrong Cannon...
It looks so authentic!
Why does everyone know
what this is?
Another name for it is
"Running Thunder."
It is a deadly weapon that caused
"The Seven Days of Flames"
during the Balkans Campaign.
That's not the story that
I heard earlier...
So what are you
doing here, huh?
I'm participating in this
contest just for fun.
Wow!
That's amazing!
It's like an amusement
park attraction!
You know, events like this should
be fun for children, as well...
You are welcome to play on it,
if you want to...
Hey, that's not the right way
to play on it.
So this is kinda like
for rock climbing?
No way!
This is a slide, Kagura!
Zoom!
Don't slide with those on!
Hey, Cobra, where are
the stairs on this?
Why do you guys have to obsess
over rock climbing?
Besides, I can see you used the
stairs half way up, you idiot!
Geez, the slide is all
scratched up now.
I'll have to smooth it
out with my spit.
You bastards!
I know what you're up to,
you're trying to ruin my work
so that you can win
the grand prize!
I won't let you win that easy!
Hey, isn't it amazing?
You must really be a genius.
How did you come up with
attaching a slide to this?
I don't know, but it just
came to me,
like I was suddenly hit
with some expiration.
You mean, inspiration.
Oh, hi.
Gintoki, hello there.
What a surprise...
I swear I had no idea
that you were here...
It's not like I was following
you or anything.
It's just that...
Nobody even asked you if...
This is a Neo Armstrong Cyclone
Jet Armstrong Cannon.
It really looks so authentic!
How can you even tell, it doesn't
look like a cannon anymore!
During the interstellar war,
between the planets Tom and Jeromy,
unlike the "Method Cannon" that
ultimately led the Jeromy's to victory,
this cursed weapon
was put in a storehouse,
and abandoned for ages.
Whatever!
That's such a long story!
So are you...
making a snow sculpture, too?
Well, yes, I am,
but it's nothing really...
Oh, seriously?
I see something over there
that could obviously
only have been made by you.
Don't get me wrong.
That‐That's not Gin at all.
Um... It is fictitious,
and any resemblance to real
persons is purely coincidental!
Yeah, its legs are far too long.
Gin's are much shorter than those.
It's a reflection of her fantasy.
Well, that's about right...
Wow, it really looks
exactly like me...
I bet this will win
the grand prize...
I can't possibly destroy
this snow statue.
What's that?
Really, are you complimenting me?
I'm just saying what I am thinking
out loud, nothing more.
Why are his arms all stretched
out like that?
Oh, well that...
is for this!
And now it's compleee...
Impossible!
What are you doing?
Gin's arms are broken!
Fix them quickly!
I'm so sorry!
Oh, my glasses, my glasses...
I'll put them right back on!
Hello there...
‐What're you doing, you dirty old geezer!
‐Oh, why me?
How strange.
I thought that you really
were touching me, Gin.
I'm so sorry.
Hello, Sis, what are you doing here?
Well...
the bar I work at is participating
in the competition.
Oh?
It's the Neo Armstrong Cyclone
Jet Armstrong Cannon.
It looks so authentic!
That's enough!
It obviously looks nothing like it!
It looks so stupid.
What a pitiful Armstrong, right?
What are you talking about?
What is this Armstrong Cannon?!
Anyway, do you want to come
and see our sculpture, Shin?
We all worked incredibly
hard on it...
See?
Isn't it great?
So tell me...
what did the Odd Jobs
team make?
Oh, well...
I'm too embarrassed...
to say what we're making, I mean,
what the hell is a
Neo Armstrong Cyclone
Jet Armstrong Cannon, anyway?
It's just some porny thing, come on.
Ah.
The truth at last.
There's no way we'd
win the grand prize,
or even a prize for participating.
Let's go home, before we publicly
humiliate ourselves.
Where are you two going?
Don't you want to stay just
to enjoy our snow statue?
What's that?
There's something weird
on the snow statue!
Who cares about the grand prize!
I've decided, that if I can't win this
contest, then nobody can win it!
And besides, all these statues
are gonna melt, anyway...
Into oblivion!
It's a pervert!!
Help us!!
All our efforts are futile!
Even if we made a new slide,
they'd simply destroy it again!
I don't want the slide anymore, anyway!
I wish all the slides in the
world would just collapse!
Oh, my!
Everybody is fighting now!
What a total mess!
What should we do, Otae?
We'd better give up on winning,
don't you think?
Otae?
Hey, what are you doing?
Who do you think you're kidding?
There's no way I'm giving
up on this grand prize!
We promised to share the 100 cups
of Bargain‐Dash ice cream,
and I'm going to win!
Bargain‐Dash?
The winner gets 100 cups
of ice cream?
Hey, you've got to be kidding me.
I worked so hard, and
on a very cold day...
because I heard there would
be a cash prize
for the winner of the contest,
I can't believe this...
Damn you...
you rotten granny,
you tricked me!
How dare you treat
us like fools!
Hey, Otose...
what were...
we doing again here again?
Is this a snowball
fight competition?
Nope...
It's a festival.
Hey, you see that?!
You see that,
I made those fireworks!!
You know, it's a little bit lopsided...
Oh, quit nitpicking
all the small things.
Fireworks sparkling
in the summer sky.
Like a flower...
that blooms for a small
moment in time...
and then fades away...
just like us...
human beings.
Uh...
Uhh...
What is this?
This just looks like a snail
to me no matter what.
Is this some kind of harassment?
This has to be that...
escargot thing we hear
legends about.
It's really expensive..
Is it really?
Hey, listen, this job
might pay really well!
After all, we haven't
even met them yet...
and they're treating us
to this kind of food!
Don't get so excited,
you simpleton!
We'll be laughing stocks
if we eat this!
They're testing our manners,
I mean look at the butler.
Right, he's smirking at us,
isn't he?
You're right...
What?
But, then what are we
supposed to do with...
this snail?
It's obviously a plate!
We put food on top of it
and then we eat it...
A plate?
But it's already on a plate!
Yeah, but coffee cups
come on plates, don't, hey?
It's more classy that
way or something.
You two are both real hicks.
Watch how I use it...
Excuse me!
More water, please.
Now, I see...
We use it to summon the butler.
That's why it's disk‐shaped.
Hey, butler!
Can I have some chopsticks, please?
Hey, Gin, I don't think that's
how you use escargot.
Yes, it is.
Because he stopped smirking.
Wait?
Is he crying?
Who's that guy?
What?
A snail fairy?
Look, he's got a snail on his head.
Do you think...
that's what we're supposed
to do with this?
I'm so sorry I'm late,
Mr. Odd Jobs.
My mother is sick and I...
What in the world are you
guys all doing?!
I'm sorry.
You see, we're not exactly
used to this kind of thing...
That's quite all right.
I'm just glad to see you've gotten
acquainted with my father already
and are getting along properly.
Your father?
Yes, believe or not...
That's actually my father...
You see, I called you over here today...
to ask you if you would
take care of him for me.
You old escargot fart!
That's my...
Who are you calling
escalator or cart?!
I'm so sorry...
but you see, my father...
hasn't exactly been himself lately...
He used to be a master of fireworks..
the greatest pyrotechnician in the
Capital and built up our household...
But ever since he retired to
take care of my ill mother,
his dementia has really set in.
Flute Sky Walker, look at you.
You're very hairy today, aren't you?
Hoot Slime Walker is cute.
That's a cute name.
‐No, no, he's Shoot Shit‐Stalker...
‐He often wanders around
in the middle of the night,
and sometimes disappears for days.
‐He's getting to be a handful...
‐Hoot Shit Lover is a pretty name.
Right, right.
But it's really Michael J. Dogs.
They seem to be getting along.
Though their conversation
is completely incoherent...
Men sure are delicate, aren't they?
Women are able to live their lives...
fairly well even after
their husbands die...
But when the wife dies first...
men start shriveling up and
they can't survive on their own,
and It's a pitiful sight.
Excuse me, but his wife
isn't dead yet...
She fell ill three years ago...
and has been bedridden
ever since...
He stopped making fireworks...
in order to take care of her...
and now he's like this...
He must have really
loved his fireworks...
It makes me feel sorry for the
old man when I think about...
You old fart!
What are you doing?!
He said he's going to
meet his mistress.
As if that exists!
He's just trying to run away!
Get down now!
What?
‐Stand aside!
‐What?
There!
We can't take our eyes off
of him for one second...
Hey, Gin...
wasn't that a bit too much?
You realize we're supposed
to take care of him...
not take his life from him, right?
Yahoooo!
Whoa!
He hasn't given up yet!
What?
Why is he so energetic?
Is he really an old man?
Hey, guys!
You're destroying
the entire house!
‐There!
Oh.
Father, I'm sick of your
ridiculous behavior!
Don't you realize
how sick mother is?
There are some things that
are just not okay to do!
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid we got
carried away, too.
No, don't you worry about it.
You guys did your very best!
Why are you talking, you old fart!
Listen, Father, but...
the doctor said mother will have
to be hospitalized...
She's gotten a lot worse.
We simply can't take care
of her at home anymore.
But so then he's going
to be separated...
from his wife then?
Father...
Don't you have anything
to say concerning this?
I'm going to see my mistress.
‐Oh.
This is just awful...
I wonder if he even
remembers my mother at all.
Please excuse me.
No, please don't go...
Please don't go after him,
and just let him be,
I'm the one who made
him that way...
I'm the one that took away his
beloved fireworks from him...
So please...
Just let him be free...
He's done more than enough
for me when I became ill...
He gave up his entire career
that he loved so much
and did everything he could
to take care of me...
But...
I can't stand to see him
so miserable
because he can't do what
he loves to do anymore...
I want him to forget about me
and return to his love...
His mind was always filled with
his love for his fireworks,
ever since the day I met him...
There was no place for me in
his heart from the very beginning...
But that is the man that
I fell in love with.
Oh, Mother...
Hey, so...
this is the place where
he hides his lover.
That's right...
And she's quite a beauty,
as well.
Please be a gentleman and
not disturb them, Mr. Sakata.
You're the butler...
So tell me, exactly what
are you doing here?
Whoa!
The old man's been really
pent‐up hasn't he!
What kind of fetish is that?
I did good...
There we go...
Fireworks, huh...
Just as I thought...
How long have you known
about this, Mr. Butler?
For..
quite a long time now...
I heard that he leaves the house
for a couple of days at a time
but it was to come here, huh?
What a man he is!
He forgets most things...
but not his fireworks, huh?
Fireworks are his entire life.
They are a part of his soul...
Even as his memory fades,
his great skills never will.
I feel bad for his wife in saying this,
but Master is an artisan before
he is a husband or a father...
I beg you, as a favor,
please leave him alone,
and let him die as the
great craftsman that he is.
He's forgotten everything...
including his very
own wife and all.
But the skills that are
hardwired into his body...
they'll never disappear, huh?
What a sad story that is, but I think.
I think humans are far
better than that...
Even if your memories
flee from your noggin...
the memories that are ingrained
deep within your heart,
within your soul,
they never disappear...
And that's what I'd like to believe.
Hey!
Are you watching?
Oh, just shut up!
Yes, I'm watching...
God, why do I have to watch
fireworks on such a cold day?!
Fireworks in winter are
something very special!
I've told you that before.
Keep your eyes propped
wide open, all right?
You say you've developed
some new techniques but...
why do I have to come and
watch your test fireworks?
I'm sure that he was trying
to say "Marry me,"
but he misspelled and it said
"Carry me" instead.
My goodness!
Father hasn't changed at all,
not a single bit.
It's as you say...
You're not cold are you, Mother?
I'm alright...
Yes...
that was fifty eight
years ago today and...
I wonder if he
still remembers...
No...
There's no way he
would remember...
Matsu!
Every year on this date,
I'll light up the sky for you!
He's such a liar.
That was the very first
and very last time
he ever made fireworks for me.
Matsu, you once said to me...
that both people and fireworks
bloom like beautiful flowers
for just a brief moment
and then they fade away...
That may be true...
But Matsu, even if it's only
for just a brief moment,
I want you to bloom by my side...
And when you fade away,
do so at my side...
and in return...
I will make flowers bloom
by your side again and again.
Hey, Mother, look!
Look over there!
Fireworks at this time
of the year!
How beautiful they are...
Fireworks in the winter...
sure are something
incredibly special.
Yes indeed...
It's a little bit lopsided as always,
but it's beautiful.
Gin!
Look!
Wow!!
It's amazing!
Was there a firework
festival today?
Hey, are you watching?
My name is Katsura...
I travel across the country to visit
all the ramen shops in Japan
to study the path of the Ramen.
I've fallen in love with your skill.
Please allow me to
be your apprentice.
The next episode,