The death match arena,
The Purgatory...
got torn down due to our rampage.
But we didn't know that it was
actually backed by the Tendo sect,
who manipulate the government.
So, are we gonna be all right?
As for the weather in Edo City...
it seems like we will see a clear
fall sky all day long.
However...
they say the weather in autumn is as
fickle as a young woman's heart...
so please don't blame me...
if it ends up being rainy instead.
And now, it's time for.
Maya Sizitzy's Dark Horoscope.
Today's unluckiest horoscope is...
the sign of the Virgo.
Everything will go wrong
for you today.
Geez, come on.
What a downer to start the day.
Especially, any Virgos
with stubble on their chin,
who are brushing their teeth
right now.
You're dying today!
What?
The lucky color that
will bring you fortune...
is red, so be sure to hide your bloody
body with something red.
What kind of luck is that?
There's nothing lucky about that at all!
Goodbye everyone.
Have a nice day!
Oh, like hell I will!
That damn show!
It's so stupid.
I mean, there's no way
that it's accurate.
If all Virgos disappeared,
then we'd be left with a society
filled with nothing but a
bunch of blood thirsty men.
Right, Okita?
Here, take this.
I wore this red loincloth
when I was a kid.
Don't you worry.
I washed it.
What do you mean,
"Don't you worry I washed it?"
Should I be worrying
about something?
Can you believe him, Hijikata?
Take this.
I used to wear this red scarf
a long time ago.
Hey, stop it.
What is this?
I mean, what happened?
Or rather, what's gonna
happen to me?
Ta‐ta‐ta‐ta‐taya!
You stinking Gorilla!
What?
Ma‐Matsudaira, is that you?
Get up, you gorilla bastard!
Get up before I count to three,
or I'll blow your balls off!
Ready?
One...
What happened to two and three?
"Number one" is the only number...
that a man needs.
To be truthful, I don't need
any other numbers in my life.
You just said "THREE" seconds!
What the hell?
Come on, now!
You can't just do anything you want
just because you're the
commissioner of police, you know!
Shut your trap, Kondo.
Because of you...
this old man's...
this old man's head might roll,
as they say.
Huh?!
What are you talking about?
I picked you guys up off the street,
how many years ago was that?
Well, I wish I could start over.
Uh.
I should never let a lot like
you into the organization,
and I wish I could redo all this.
Ah.
And if I had the ability to do so,
I'd like to start again...
from scratch, from back when you were
still in your dad's ball sack.
What's that supposed to mean?
I told you.
I said to stay out of trouble.
I already knew you guys were morons,
but I never thought you'd get involved
with the Purgatory, that's for sure.
Huh?
Pervert Story?
I mean I love adult flicks, but I don't
remember getting involved with one.
No, you, moron!
‐Don't shoot!
I would've promoted you
if that was the case!
My goodness!
I still have a mortgage to pay!
So say goodbye to my
daughter studying abroad
and my wife's beauty salon!
What are you gonna
to do about this, huh?
What?
The Tendo sect?
I, I heard a rumor that the
Tendo sect controls the,
Shogun and that it is the real secret
power behind the government!
Is that really true?
Don't talk so damn loud!
And yeah, that's right!
They control the Shogun...
and yes, they are real power
behind the Government!
Now who's being loud?
So you're confirming the rumor.
I'm saying that you were
causing a ruckus...
and that it was deep in
their territory! Huh?
What?
You're telling me
right now we caused
a ruckus deep in the
Tendo sect's territoy?
Hey, hey, you're so transparent.
I know you're pretending that you don't
know.
How 'bout I shoot you, huh?
Should I?
Th‐They did this.
They did it while I was gone.
So, you mean, that we were
called in by the Tendo Sect...
to be punished?
I bet we're an eyesore for them,
but I don't think they'd
do that to us right now.
Doing anything to us publicly
will be the same as admitting
they were involved
with the Purgatory and
that whole mess.
We're in great danger more than
that at this moment.
They might be calling us
to the castle
in order to get the two of us
together and then...
Boom!
It would be a perfect opportunity.
The sign of the Virgo.
You're dying today!
And...
then, they can just blame it
all on the Exclusionist Rebels.
I wanna go home now!
What do you think you are you doing?
Let go!
I don't want to die with an
ugly old coot like you!
No, I want to die on Otae 's lap!
You idiot!
You know the way of Samurai
is found in Death!
No way!
I would rather live my hairy life,
because I love my hairy ass!
Listen!
If we work together, we might
be able to reach the castle alive.
If we can do that, we win!
They can't kill us publicly if
we get to the castle first.
‐We'll survive!
‐We'll survive?
Maybe.
Mommy, I'm coming home!
Calm down!
We're all gonna die eventually.
But the important thing
is how you live your life!
No way!
I want to live a fun and kinky life!
It all depends on your fortune.
So believe in your fortune.
Fortune...
Hey old man...
Tell me, what's your horoscope sign?
Huh?
I'm a Virgo, why?
Oh God, we're doomed!
It's 100 percent certain
that we're all going to die!
‐It's a death drive!
‐Calm down!
‐It's hopeless!
‐If you don't, I'll snag a booger
‐It's hopeles!
‐from your big nose and shove it...
‐I wanna go home!
‐back up into your stupid brain!
‐Shut up!
I can't believe you're a Virgo!
You don't act like a virgo at all!
Your horoscope must be a
mobster or something.
Yes, you're definitely a mobster!
I don't want to hear
that from you, Kondo!
Why don't I shoot you
into space right now?
Then you can be a brand
new horoscope, Gorilles!
‐No, no way!
‐You two, please calm down...!
Let me go!
Let go!
Hey, hey, hey!
Look where you're going when you're
driving!
Give me a break!
All right?
You are an assassin, aren't you?
Yes, you're an assassin, right?
Say it!
I bet you're an assassin.
What?!
What are you talking about?
I'm.
Hey, you pops!
Are you crazy?
Come on, what the hell
are you thinking?
Hey, let me drive now.
It's a war zone from here on out.
You go on home now.
A‐a‐all right.
Hey, Boss, but what are you doing?
He looked like a normal man to me!
You idiot!
The guy was wearing sunglasses,
wasn't he?
Definitely an assassin.
Huh?
Anyone who wears sunglasses is
an assassin, 99% of the time.
But you're wearing sunglasses, too!
This secret is just between you and me.
You know Stevie Wonder, the singer?
He's also an assassin.
So is the world‐famous Kurosawa,
Michael Jackson,
and also John Lennon.
But don't tell anyone this.
I couldn't tell anyone!
It's just a delusional old man's
stupid imaginations!
Hey.
He's still alive!
Hello.
Excuse me.
I'm late because.
I dropped my glasses
on the way over.
Who the heck are you?
I don't know.
Without my glasses on,
I can't see anything,
I can't see where I'm standing
or where I'm heading to.
Hey...
now get a hold of yourself!
Oh!
Are you the driver's pet?
Like a gorilla?
What kind of gorilla are you?
Like that car, Gorilla Mark II?
Oh, you like that?
Good boy.
I'm a human being, not a gorilla.
Don't you worry, she's on our side.
This is Sacchan.
Here, hold onto this, Saccchan.
She's my old friend.
She's a freelance contract
killer right now...
but she used to be an elite
secret agent.
Because as everyone knows.
To kill an assassin, one needs
to use an assassin!
Matsudaira, what's this?
I can't see clearly, what is it?
Hey, watch out with that!
Oh?
A peppermint dispenser?
Peppermint is great for
reducing sleepiness
and preventing bad breath, here!
Stop!
That's not going to stop bad breath,
it'll stop your breath period!
It's such a weird shape, isn't it?
How do I get the peppermint out,
do I press here?
Stop that!
I'll give you something better than
a peppermint, so please!
Stop!
Don't touch me!
My heart already belongs
to another man!
‐Let me go!
‐Geez!
Why is this person
even here with us?
Shut up!
Enough yelling!
You're distracting me!
W‐Watch out!
H‐Hey, Pops!
Did we hit something?
Hey, Boss!
You just hit something!
It just went flying!
Yeah, that was an assassin as well.
No way, you liar!
You just made that up!
You know what they say...
you can't make an omelette
without breaking an assassin.
You there, just shut up!
Who is this guy?
Why is he ordering me around?
There's only one person
in the world
who can order me around
or tie me up.
But how strange.
I find I'm beginning to love hearing
his harsh words.
Please just shut the hell up!
Pretty please!
Now what is this?
"Pretty please?"
You shifted your gear to reverse?
You're too complicated.
But I'll try to understand.
You're not even close!
You're totally clueless!
Like a teenage girl trying on
make up for the first time!
You have hurt Elizabeth!
And I will not forgive you.
No!
So you've come for me
at last, assassin!
We're scraping the wall!
Sparks!
On both sides of the car!
Do you see...
my special driving technique?
That's no technique!
All I'm hearing is squeak and shriek!
Come on, Kondo, and shut up.
Hey!
Look!
Look out ahead!
Don't worry, I'm Schumacher, you know!
That was close.
The assassin totally wrecked the car!
Assassin?
Where is he?
Where's the assasin?
You totally crashed the car yourself!
You know, a kind person
takes all the blame,
and ends up hurting himself.
What are you going to do now?
Because now we don't have
any transportation.
Huh?
Hee, hoo, hee, hoo, hee, hoo, hee, hoo,
hee, hoo, hee, hoo, hee, hoo, hee, hoo,
hee, hoo, hee, hoo...
That is a...
This is an emergency.
We should commandeer that bicycle.
Wait, where are you going!
I have a bad feeling about that bicycle.
It's punishment!
It's punishment, right?
Because I want to be punished!
I love Punishment!
Cut it out, already, crazy lady!
What a mess this whole situation is!
For the sake of those poor innocent
people who gave us this bike,
we have to get to the
castle alive, no matter what!
Hee hoo, hee hoo, hee hoo,
hee hoo I wonder why?
All of a sudden, I can see nothing
but darkness ahead.
Is this a reflection of my soul?
When did it become so dark?
Huh?
No!
Sacchan don't give in
to the darkness!
If you can't find a backdoor,
you have to
make one for yourself!
You have to!
Right there!
Aaaaah!
It disappeared!
My darkness disappeared!
I'm done.
I am so done.
I should've just gone home.
Hm?..
What the heck is that over there?
It's just a sad bunch of
edgy attention seekers
who think they're on a
vacation riding a bike.
At least they aren't causing
anyone any trouble.
I really don't know what to do about
those losers living above my bar.
They come up with so many
excuses to not pay their rent!
But my patience is wearing thin
and is about to reach its limit!
You're acting as if they
owe you the rent!
Hey, Kondo.
Do you see them?
They are assassins.
What?
There's no way, come on!
Can't you see it, Kondo?
Look at their dark auras.
There's no doubt.
Yes, I can see it as well.
What?
Their postures.
Only those who carry
the deepest sorrows
within can strike that kind of pose.
What the hell are you talking about?
I can't see it, so come on, guys!
Let's kill them before they kill us!
This is..
a pedestrian road!
Yes, Ma'am.
Well, things like this happen.
No way!
I was just so scared of them!
I thought I might piss my pants
at this old age you know.
Yeah, well, your eyes are certainly
pissing alright.
There, there, fluffy things!
How many of them would you like,
Mr. Amanto?
G, all of them.
Get every last one of them.
You manage to act like a jobless loser
who never leaves his mommy's nest.
Well done, Prince!
They're so fluffy!
So cute!
I finally found you, assassin.
Seriously.
I can't keep up with this crap.
W‐What are you doing?!
Don't you know, I'm Prince Hata!
‐Prince Kaka?
‐Not Kaka!
It's Prince Hata.
Hata!
G! Do something!
Sir!
Umm so...
I'm so sorry!
You can take him,
but please spare me!
All right.
But in exchange, can I take your car?
Of course, if you let me live!
Hey!
Wha?
We don't have time.
Hurry up!
All right!
Why did you let those two go?
I thought they're assasins.
Well, they were just small fries.
Hi, fancy seeing you here!
You're shopping here, too?
What a surprise to see you
in this kind of place.
As I thought, you and I are
destined to be together, Otae!
Oh,my goodness.
Looks like a gorilla has
escaped from the zoo.
I should call the Exterminators
and have it shot dead ASAP.
Let's see, their catch phrase is.
"Call us and they're dead
as a Dodo, we promise!"
Otae, please!
Are you kidding me right now?
It's me, Kondo!
It's your Kondo!
Such a bad gorilla!
He's threatening me!
You should know your place, gorilla!
Now I'm going to show you!
Today's unluckiest horoscope is.
The sign of a Virgo.
You're dying today!
I die today...
Stop it Sis!
He's not a gorilla!
He's Kondo!
Not a gorilla at all!
Oh my, if it isn't Kondo
all of a sudden.
It was always him, Sis.
It was Kondo from the start!
I'll shoot you if you don't start driving
by the time I finish counting to ten.
Ten.
You didn't even count!
You just missed me!
So close!
Otae, what did you just say?
Do you really wish I was dead?
No way!
I've got it!
This breadstick is
from Olive Garden!
This barbeque sauce is
from Outback Steakhouse.
And this dip is from Red Lobster.
I see they've changed the recipe.
You're so amazing, Kagura!
Call me "Ultimate Tongue."
Running out of gas?
I bet you're an assassin, too!
Yeah.
We'll be replaced by this gorilla before
‐we knew it.
‐B‐Boss!
Please calm down, I beg you.
It's my last wish!
My last wish!
Really?
Just how many "last wishes"
do you have, then?
It's my first wish!
My first wish!
Hey!
That's it!
Whoa!
Let's go, amazing gorilla power!
Oooh.
Oh, no.
And now he's admitted
that he is a gorilla.
Well, I guess it's better for him to
realize who he really is.
Hey! How can you guys
just relax back there?
You can't run from your sins,
you know.
Face your death!
Oh, my!
What a giant peppermint.
With a size this large, it can save
the entire city from bad breath.
Whoa!
It's a bomb!
Throw it!
Hurry!
Where are my glasses?
I need my glasses.
‐I need my glasses to.
‐Just throw it already!
Here we go!
Get down everyone!
Huh?
Oh! it's you.
‐OH!
Holy.
Eh?
What?
Was that my booger?
Did my booger just do that?
It's time, Kondo.
Commissioner of National Police,
Katakuriko Matsudaira.
And Shinsengumi chief, Isao Kondo.
Here, at your service, sirs!
Yes.
Very good.
Today, I've called you here
because of the incident
that occurred the other day
regarding the underground arena,
the Purgatory.
Did something happen to you two?
Nothing.
Just some trouble baking
some pecan pies.
So you got into another fight,
did you?
All Samurai are very brave, after all.
I've heard it only took
thirty of your men
to take down the Purgatory.
There're so many cowardly samurai
around these days, but you
did an awesome job.
Yes...
you and your men were
quite impressive.
Thanks to you,
we have maintained
a serene balance
between the Amanto
and the Earthlings.
I commend you both.
But you'd better not rush too
fast to obtain victory.
I understand your sense of justice,
but if you start biting at everything,
you might end up biting tails of wolves
and get your head chewed off,
do you understand what I'm saying?
Piss off the big guys,
and they'll wipe you all out,
so you'd better take our advice.
If you want to live a long life,
you'd better learn to be smart.
Well, it seems we survived somehow.
Well yeah.
I think we had been misunderstanding
their intentions all along.
That was a really fierce fight.
One of the top five closest
calls of my entire life.
Hey, Pops,
I feel like I would've made it to the
castle with no problems whatsoever
if I hadn't been with you.
Yeah, well let's make sure this is the
last time we're in this situation, huh?
I have enough problems at home,
you know.
My daughter has a new boyfriend
who cross dresses and it's messing with my head.
This will be the last chance
for you because...
if something like this
happens again, you are..
Yeah... I understand.
I'm sorry I caused you
so much trouble, Boss.
We'll make sure we won't
get caught the next time.
Heh...
As long as you understand.
Oh, yeah right, the horoscope.
Just as I thought, that was
a phony horoscope!
"Virgos will die" bullshit!
Oh!
There she is!
‐Otae!
‐Oh, Big Sis! Come on!
What a coincidence
to see you again!
I'd never expected
to find you here.
You're right, Kondo.
What a coincidence!
Ahh!
Health, health me!
What's the matter, Kagura?
Something black and shiny
is in my room, Gintoki!
Hey, how can you be the
strongest girl in space
and be scared by
something like that?
The next episode...
Hey, Shinpachi.
Take a look behind you!