Gin, Gin, you won't believe this!
What's up, Mr. four eyes?
The guy who was stalking
my sister!
He's Isao Kondo, the bureau chief
of the Shinsengumi!
Yeah, I already knew that.
But who did you hear it from?
‐From Johnny.
‐From Johnny?
Yeah, Johnny.
Hey, auntie.
Give me some pickled seaweed!
Come again.
Doo doo doo,
dee doo doo...
‐Whoa!
What the hell is with its size?
It's huge!
There's no way it's real!
What are you doing hanging around
the front of my place, you brats?
Did you find a dirty magazine
or something?
Ah! It's the weird seaweed girl!
Run away, or you'll smell
fishy just like her!
Those little brats can go home
and suck their moms' teats.
All right, now let's hear a special report
from the Sky Terminal.
Maya Sizitzy is on the scene!
Maya Sizitzy!!
Yes, Maya Sizitzy at the scene.
Here at the Sky Terminal,
hordes of reporters have
gathered and they are all
eagerly waiting the arrival of the ship
that is carrying Prince Hata.
Oh, the gate at the Sky Terminal
is opening!
It seems that Prince Hata's spaceship
has finally arrived.
During his return visit to Edo City,
Prince Kaka...
uh, I mean, Prince Hata plans to visit
the newly constructed Edo Zoo,
followed by more visits to
many other zoos and aquariums.
Oh, there he is!
Prince Hata of the Midland Star
has stepped out of his spaceship
and he is waving to us!
It's been a very long time,
everyone!
I'm so overjoyed.
No need for formalities.
No need at all.
Oh, the Prince!
Who did that to him?
Was it you
or was it you?
‐It was you, wasn't it?
‐I'm pretty sure that it was you.
That's all, at least for now.
Maya Sizitzy reporting
from the scene.
Apparently that stupid
animal obsessed prince
has come back to Edo City.
How about that, Gin?
Hey, man,
are you listening to me?
I'm back, everyone!
Oh! Welcome back, Kagura.
Did you get the toilet paper
that I asked you for?
Here you go.
Okay, Kagura, listen up.
Usually people buy toilet paper
in packs of several rolls, okay?
If someone gets diarrhea
there's no way
this will ever be enough.
Quit nagging me about
the toilet paper, Shinpachi!
What are you,
my mother‐in‐law?
After all, there are poor
samurai in this world
who pretend newspapers
are toilet papers, you know!
I don't think anyone
is that desperate!
Who told you that anyway?
Gin told me!
Ask him!
How many times have I told you
not to trust what he says?
Shut up, will ya?
Don't act like a know it all
when you barely have hair
on your balls, you idol otaku!
What did you say to me?
Aren't you younger than me?
So, have some respect!
Shinpachi, what's that white thing
over there?
What does it look like?
It's toilet paper, obviously.
Not that!
I mean the big thing!
Can you stop saying
perverted stuff like
the "big thing" or
the "little thing" all the time?
You know It's because of
that potty mouth of yours
that Kagura is also
always being so...
What the hell is that?
Someone dropped it outside.
Isn't it just so cute?
Nobody dropped it!
If you're gonna pick
something up,
at least make it something
that we know the name of!
Sadaharu.
You just named it that!
You totally made
that name up just now!
By the way, this was stuck
to his collar.
Let's see.
"To Odd Jobs Gin.
I am very sorry
about doing this,
but can you please
take care of my pet?"
So is that all it says?
Then it says, "L. O. L."
in parenthesis.
L.O.L. my ass!
I'm "M. A. D." in parenthesis!
In other words, that thing
was abandoned at our door!
We may do odd jobs, but we're not
some kind of charity!
Get rid of it!
No way, Gin!
If we abandon him
all alone out there
in this cold and heartless
town, then he might die!
Don't you worry
your little head.
I'm sure Sadaharu will be able
to manage on his own.
What do you know
about Sadaharu anyway?
You understand,
don't you, Sadaha...
Oh, just as I expected!
Earth is so fun!
Perhaps it's because
of this nice environment,
but there are so many
different living creatures here!
I'm never tire
of coming here, right, G?
I couldn't agree more,
Your Highness.
The last time I came to Edo City,
I endured all kinds of terrible abuses!
But this time, I want to check out
all of the zoos in Edo City
to take some unusual creatures
back home with us.
Right, G?
Oh man, what a pain
in the butt.
Did you say something?
No, I didn't say anything at all,
Prince Kaka.
You just called me Prince Kaka.
Who just called him
Prince Kaka?
Was it you?
‐Oh, it was you, wasn't it?!
‐I'm pretty sure that it was you.
Admit it!
This is the Ultra giraffe,
which was found on Nebula M78.
Such a cute creature!
By the way, the Ultra giraffe
eats people.
This is the Iskandar elephant
from the Large Magellanic Clouds.
Oh! This one is very cute too!
By the way, when it
stretches out its trunk...
it eats people too.
This is the petit penguin,
which inhabits Lilliput Planet.
Uh, this one had better
not eaten people.
The petit penguin does not
eat people, Prince.
However, the white polar bear
below does eat people.
Are you trying to have me
killed or what?
Say, Vice Chief Hijikata,
why do we have
to be the ones
who are always out here
looking for some animal?
I don't really know, Okita.
But I hear that they're using it
to get on the good side
of some VIP who's visiting
the city of Edo.
Well, if it's to get on
the good side of some VIP
we don't even know.
Then, I guess any animal we catch
should be good enough
to please them, am I right?
So, by any animal...
what you are actually
trying to say is...
What the hell do you think
you're doing, Okita?
Just doing my duty to suck up
to some visiting VIP.
Do you have a death wish
or something?
So then, can you give me
a good bow‐wow?
Screw you!
What's this?
So the thing is, until we can find
a new owner to adopt him,
I will allow Shigeo to stay
here in our home.
His name isn't Shigeo!
His name's Sadaharu.
But as soon as we find another owner,
I can assure you
that Tatsunori is totally
out of here!
Enough, stop changing it's name!
But look at how cute
Sadaharu is!
How come you don't like him,
Gin, huh?
Because men just can't trust anything
that women say is cute.
Shinpachi, are you like that too?
By day you're a four‐eyed otaku
acting like you're into cutesy girls,
but by night you chase
after sexy loose women?
Who are you calling
a four‐eyed otaku?
‐Anyway, just try petting him!
‐Oh! No, down boy!
‐I'm sure you'll be convinced...
‐I don't want to pet him!
...that he's cute!
Go ahead!
‐So?
‐Get...
get him off of me, Kagura.
This thing is so heavy!
So now you understand
how heavy my heart feels?
No, that's not
what he meant, Kagura.
Being loved is
a very heavy burden, indeed.
But don't worry, because Sadaharu
and I will be okay!
I... I can't breathe.
I think the chocolate pastry
I just ate
is about to be squeezed out
of both ends of my body.
‐No, no! I'm not into that!
‐No, enough of that!
‐Stop, it hurts!
‐No, no!
Can't they chill for
one freaking minute...
Hey, you stupid punks!
Quit tearing the place apart!
Kagura, hey!
You need to discipline him
with training!
I don't mind if he misbehaves.
He can grow naturally
and learn naturally!
You two misbehaving is going to
end up with people dying naturally!
What just happened, Gin?
That Sadaharu just went and
squeezed out a number one
right on top of the comic
that I was reading!
Squeezed out a number one?
I'm so proud of you!
He also squeezed out
a huge number two
right on top of
Otsu's debut album!
Otsu, featuring
Sadaharu's Number 2!
Sadaharu, you are going
to pay for...!
‐Sorry.
‐Sorry about that.
Hello.
Hell must have frozen over
if you're here.
I'm not lending you any money.
That's not it.
I just came here
to pay you the rent.
What kind of prank is this?
There must be a hidden camera
somewhere in here.
It's nothing like that!
I just thought that at least
I'd pay you this month's rent, ah?
I guess the heat must've
gotten to your head.
Hey, hold it!
Come on!
This is that famous dog
Clifford's second cousin!
He should be worth
at least a month's rent!
I don’t want it even if
it’s Lassie’s brother!
Wait for me!
Okay, here's the plan.
While Kagura is taking a nap,
we'll go look for another owner
to adopt Sadaharu ourselves.
Wait, that is the plan?
Are you sure?
Kagura is going to be
very angry with us.
It's all right.
By experiencing harsh reality,
a young girl grows up
to become a lady.
And an idol otaku
graduates from fandom.
What are you talking about?
Are you talking about me?
No way, I'm never graduating!
Okay, let's go!
Hey!
Come on, move it!
Let's go, you giant
poop machine!
Good boy, good boy...
This thing should be
around here somewhere.
‐Hijikata.
‐Huh?
What are you doing, Okita?
I think you should
probably watch out.
Huh?
What was that?
It's that guy again?
Sadaharu?
He's finally settled down.
So what are we
gonna do now?
I doubt there's anyone around
who would want to adopt Sadaharu.
Don't worry, Shinpachi.
I have an idea.
He squeezed one out again!
This is your idea?
It's my house!
Are you planning to dump
Sadaharu on us?
Oh, you know how it is.
Your sister has been having trouble
with a stalker, right?
Gin, you already took care of that stalker
the other day, remember that?
Real friends help each other
out in times of need.
He'll be the perfect
guard dog for her.
Will you just listen to me,
damn it?
Will you stop biting?
Oh! What exactly are you two
doing out here?
Sheesh! Where did Sadaharu
and Gin run off to?
So, you think that you could
take this dog off our hands?
We already have one useless
adolescent boy living in this house.
So, for us to take in one more,
I'm not so sure.
Was "useless" really
necessary to say?
Besides, sis, this is a dog
we're talking about!
Look, seriously, please!
Even if Sadaharu is saying
that he wants to stay here.
What do you mean
he wants to stay here?
Damn!
Taking him away
behind my back?
No, no, no!
You've got it all wrong.
‐This is for Sadaharu's sake.
‐You are terrible, Gin!
‐Oh, come on.
‐Oh my!
I think that he likes you
quite a lot.
Sadaharu!
Come and chase me, boy!
Geez, they get along
like milk and cookies,
and it makes you want
to smile, huh, Shinpachi?
Yeah, sure.
I guess girls and big goofy dogs
are a match made in heaven.
I wonder why that dog
just won't take to us?
It knows that we're trying
to get rid of him.
It can tell by
it's animal instinct, Gin.
But why is it so attached
to her, Shinpachi?
It isn't really attached to her, Gin.
It's trying to kill her, but Kagura thinks
that it's just being playful.
Cut it out, silly!
I understand.
‐So that's how it is, Shinpachi?
‐Yeah.
At least somebody's having fun.
You know what?
I really love animals.
All girls really love
cute things, you know,
so no further explanation is needed.
You call that thing cute?
Of course, it's cute!
This is the first time an animal
has gotten so attached to me!
Oh, Kagura, please realize
what's going on.
I used to have a pet
a long time ago,
Sadaharu No.1.
Sadaharu No.1 was really cute,
and I just loved him so much.
I kept Sadaharu No.1 outside,
but one night I really,
really wanted to sleep with him,
so I snuggled with him in my bed
without telling my parents.
But then, I had a nightmare and
thrashed around all night long.
It was terrible, and when
I finally woke up,
Sadaharu was as stiff as a rock.
I don't know if I'm supposed
to be laughing or crying at this.
After that happened, I swore I'd never
get close to animals ever again.
I'm not good at controlling my strength,
so I only end up hurting them.
But maybe, if it's Sadaharu,
he and I can be together
without anyone getting hurt.
He is a gift from the heavens.
‐I'm sure of it, cute dog.
‐Oh!
Oh, I forgot that I'm all out
of pickled seaweed.
I'm gonna go and buy some.
Take care of Sadaharu for me!
Be right back!
Hey, come back here!
Hey, Sadaharu!
Stop it!
‐Gin, Gin, Gin, help!
‐Wait!
Gin, help me!
Help me, Gin!
And I'm saved!
He looks cute when
he's sleeping like that though.
He's a demon
in a dog's clothing.
We're living in a crazy world
with vicious dogs.
We have to keep
a grip on our sanity.
But after seeing
how much Kagura loves it,
I feel kinda bad
for how things are going.
Oh, so there you are.
Oh, it's you guys again.
What do you want now?
Don't you have a day job to do?
Are you looking for
some play date or something?
As if I'd ever invite you out!
Inviting you to a fight
is more like it!
You remember the last fight
that you picked with me?
Well, you just turned tail
and ran away.
Bring it on, sucker!
Let me send you to a hospital,
but with no tails or legs.
By the way, Bossman...
is that your giant dog
over there?
No, it's not really my giant dog.
But why are you asking?
Who said you could change
the subject, huh?
Listen, there's a certain someone
connected to the government big shots
who's interested
in animals like that.
We would like you to hand
that dog over to the Shinsengumi.
Forget it, man.
I wouldn't give it
to guys like you.
You can tell your big shots that I don't
work alongside the Shinsengumi.
Stop acting like
I'm not standing right here!
Oh, damn!
What will we do, Okita?
I think you'll just going to have to learn
how to say, "bow‐wow" after all.
Oh, shut up!
Hey Gin, did you refuse them
for Kagura's sake?
As if I would.
I just don't like being told
what to do by those guys.
Huh?
Whoa!
Oh, It's so hard to find an animal
that really catches my fancy.
Every one of them is lacking
in some way or another.
I couldn't agree more,
Your Highness.
Isn't there anything
that can be done?
Look out!
G!
What have you done?
Please calm down, my Prince!
I shall go and find us a time machine
to fix this for starters.
G, will you just calm down?!
Oh my!
What is this here?
What's the matter, my Prince?
Hey, G, look at this!
Did you find
a time machine to fix this?
No, you stupid old geezer!
This is a Dog God!
What is such a rare
species doing here?
‐Well, do you have any rope?
‐Huh?
Should we be doing this,
my Prince?
We're behaving like
common criminals here.
It's called conservation!
I can't allow such a precious
specimen to run wild!
‐All right, let's go!
‐Sure!
I've finally added an animal
to my collection!
Doo doo dooo dee doodoo...
Sadaharu!
The last time I was here, I had a horrible
time with that silver haired man
and that weirdly strong girl.
But this will finally ease the pain
of losing my darling Pesu.
Right, G?
I couldn't agree more, your...
A zombie man!
Hey, could you stop
the car, moron?
I... It's you from the last time!
I gave it a lot of thought,
but I can't let you
have this thing after all.
This thing...
She's really taken
a mad liking to it.
What are you
blabbering on about?
Move it!
I can't see a thing in
front of me, damn it!
What?
What's the matter?
A weird girl is approaching
at tremendous speed!
Give Sadaharu back!
Who the heck is Sadaharu?
Stay back!
I forgot that Sadaharu...
was on the car.
Sadaharu!
I have...
I have gone
and done it again.
I did it all over again.
Excuse me, miss.
Why are you looking
so glum, Kagura?
Oh, Gin and Sadaharu!
Sadaharu!
Sadaharu, I'm so glad!
I'm so... so glad
that you're safe!
But Gin, you were so
against keeping him before.
Whatever, Kagura.
But if you're gonna keep it,
you take care of it.
I'll be deducting
the cost of his food
from your salary though!
Thank you so much, Gintoki.
Though you've never
actually paid me my salary.
Let's not come back
to Earth anymore.
I couldn't agree more,
Your Highness.
Remember to say bow‐wow,
Chief Kondo.
You want us to find a poster girl
from a dumpling shop?
Heh! And you're telling me
it's been fifty years?
Listen, pops.
Even if we do find her, her poster
girl days will have been long over!
The next episode...