The land of the samurai.
There was a time,
a long time ago,
when our country
was called by that name.
With the arrival of...
Hang on! Can't we just skip
this narration already?
Yeah, I'm really getting sick of it.
Oh, but there might be people
watching this for the first time.
Don't bother.
It's a world they wouldn't understand
even if we explained it, anyway.
They can follow along
at their own pace.
As they say,
"Insolence is bliss!"
Not knowing the word ignorance
proves that you're real!
Pesu! Pesu!
I am very sorry, Sir.
We looked for him everywhere,
but we couldn't find him.
It appears that he is no longer
on these grounds.
Are you joking?
But, chief!
Do you think "we couldn't find him"
is going to cut it?
But... but we...
I don't need your back talk,
Hasegawa.
You Edo officials
have just one job,
and that's to shut up
and do as we tell you!
Use whatever means necessary
to find him, you useless swine!
Oh, Pesu! Pesu!
You heard me!
Now get moving!
Yes.
Sorry, sir.
‐Pesu!
‐But, chief!
We must prevent word of this
from leaking to the upper
echelons no matter what.
Yes, I know,
and I have a plan.
Enough, you useless
mop top punk!
You're gonna pay me every last penny
of all the rent that you owe,
and you'll pay me me today!
Yeah, I heard you,
I heard you.
Guess I don't have a choice.
Here it is.
Adios.
Hold on! What do you think
you're doing handing me 53 cents?
You're not buying a comic book,
you worthless punk!
That's all I have!
I said that's all I have!
Try to understand that much,
you old bat!
If you don't have money,
why don't you go and swindle
a rich old hag or two?
Man up and grow a pair,
mop top!
All you ever care about
is money, money, money.
How petty are you?
If you want someone to seduce you,
why don't you just say so...
‐...you thirsty old hag?!
‐What?
If you just wanted to get with me,
you should've said so from the start!
Gross!
If you're trying to make me puke,
I'd be happy to oblige you!
‐You want a flood of complaints...
‐Hey, chief, that's the place.
...from the very start
of this episode?
Look, I'll just wait
one more day!
If you still can't pay the rent,
then you're out of here for real!
Let's go.
What are you going to do?
She even took the 53 cents you were
going to spend on your comics.
You better pay me
this month's wages, anyway.
I'm counting on you.
It's tough enough trying to survive
on what little I have.
Like surviving a train ride with
the smelly breath of old guys.
‐Shinpachi?
‐Yes?
You don't have a girlfriend
at all, do you?
What's this, all of a sudden?
Are you interested in going out
with an older woman at all?
Otose is single and available.
No freaking way!
What do you take me for?
I'm a young man
in the prime of my youth!
Don't get your panties
bunched up, man.
The thing about money,
is that it doesn't come to guys
who really want or need it.
It only comes to people
who seem pleasant
but only try to cause mayhem
in the lives of others.
Well, that would be
you two then!
You two alone cause more mayhem
and chaos than anyone else I know!
Come on!
The tube is on the fritz.
Oh, it's coming in.
Maya Sizitzy is at the scene!
Hello, Maya!
Hello, this is Maya Sizitzy
at the scene.
It appears that the mysterious
giant organism
that appeared at Oedo Hot Spa
has destroyed the facilities
in the area
over the course
of the last several hours,
only to mysteriously disappear.
Hey, hey, another mysterious alien
got out of the Sky Terminal again.
There have been
quite a few recently.
Come on, guys!
Right now, whats more
important than the alien
is how we're going
to manage our finances.
‐What?
That old hag!
If it's about the money, I already told
you I don't have any, you rotten hag!
What's that?
Hey, chief!
What's your problem?
What do you think you're doing?
Sorry about that,
my mistake.
I'll come back another time.
Hold it!
You're the Odd Jobs man, right?
That's why you're coming with us.
Sorry to disappoint you guys,
but my mother always told me
that it's not wise to follow strangers.
Didn't she also teach you that
it was not wise to disobey the law?
You're with the government?
We are with
the Immigration Bureau,
and we came here to hire you
for a job, Mr. Odd Jobs.
When you say Taizo Hasegawa
of the Immigration Bureau,
you're talking about that big
shot government official
who oversees all
Amanto immigration?
A big shot?
Does that mean he has
a big schlong?
He's got an enormous one.
No, it means he is
an important person.
And you know, Kagura,
you really shouldn't be saying
such things like that in a show.
At any rate, what do you think a
government bigwig wants with us?
What do you want with us,
Mr. Big Schlong?
Odd Jobs Gin, was it?
I heard there were some people
who would do anything
as long as I paid
the right price.
So, I've come to ask you
to do a job.
Do a job for you?
I didn't know you guys
even worked at all.
Look around town man,
because the Amanto are doing
whatever they please.
That's pretty harsh, man.
We're doing everything we can
these days, you know.
Besides, the Capital has developed this
far primarily thanks to those aliens.
On top of that, they really seem
to like this place.
We can't be reckless.
The Amanto already have their networks
rooted in the heart of the government.
So it's best to stop dreaming about
driving them off of the Earth one day.
The only option we have left is to try to
coexist with them to protect our kind.
Coexist, eh?
And do you honestly enjoy
doing your job?
Well, never mind.
So, what do you want us
to do then?
Uh? Well, it's a job that
we can't carry out in the open.
If it becomes public,
the government will lose face.
The fact is that the government is
currently in a diplomatic crisis
that could have a decisive influence
on the future of our entire country.
Prince Hata from theo Midland Star
is staying in the Capital.
And the prince happens
to have a small problem.
My precious pet, my dear Pesu, seems
to have disappeared somewhere.
Might I ask you
to collect him for me?
Hey, hold on you three!
You guys are
the Odd Jobs right?
You're supposed to do
anything, right?
No, I know!
I know how you feel!
But take the job, please!
Shut up or I'll break your shades,
you ugly government dirt bag.
And I'll yank off
your sad little beard.
Fine, you can break my glasses,
yank off my beard,
but just take the job!
We're seriously in trouble here.
Our government borrowed quite
a bit of money from his country,
if you catch my drift.
Why would I care about that?
It's your problem.
If this country's going to collapse
because of a mere pet,
then, it should collapse then.
What do you mean by
a "mere pet"?
Pesu is like a member
of the family.
Then, please look for
your pet yourself, Prince Kaka.
Hey! It’s Prince Hata, not Prince Kaka!
You should forget those
who walk out on you,
and prepare for a new love.
That's what an independent woman
of this day and age would do.
Listen to me!
He wasn't dumped,
and he isn't a woman!
He may be a pinhead,
but he's still a prince!
‐He's still a prince!
‐Yes he's a pinhead...
...but he's still a prince, right?
That's right.
A pinhead, but still a prince!
I get it.
A pinhead, but still a prince, eh?
So like I said,
he's a pinhead prince.
Listen to me!
He's a pinhead,
but he's still a prince.
You peasants!
It's disrespectful to call
the Pinhead Prince a pinhead!
But you just called me
a pinhead as well.
Can't you handle a problem
like this all by yourselves?
Why hire us?
Well, the thing is, we have
our reasons for needing help,
but we also figured it would be
right up Mr. Odd Jobs' alley.
No, we may be called Odd Jobs,
but we haven't lost
sight of ourselves
to the point where we would wag
our tails for the government officials
and do their errands for them.
Let's go, Shinpachi,
Kagura.
See ya, Big Schlong.
Just so you three know, we intended
to compensate you very generously.
Well then, what do we
have to do?
We are prepared to do
anything you say, master!
Talk about a quick transition?
You guys are such sellouts!
What I want you to try to find is
this octopus like alien named Pesu.
It's probably wandering
around the city.
I want you to capture it unharmed and
bring it back here before tomorrow.
Do you really think Pesu
would be in the harbor
just because it looks
like an octopus?
It doesn't matter anyway.
It can be anything.
All we need is one hook,
and we can go from there.
It’s like speed‐dating parties.
Mm... octopus jars!
You know fishermen set those up
and just wait for the octopus.
Are you some emo teen
who can't confess his love?
Waiting around doesn't find you love
nor will it help you find an octopus.
Stop saying silly crap
and let's go.
I know a lot about sea octopuses,
but I don't know anything
about land octopuses.
Why not ask a shop
that sells land octopuses?
These dumplings have
octopus inside,
but I've never seen one
that looks like this.
Hey, Sabu, ever seen an octopus
that looks like this?
Yeah.
I think I saw something like that
at the shop on the main street.
What? You wanted something
from me?
‐Pesu!
Okay, I get it,
but no way!
Come on, don't you think they look
kinda similar here around the eyes?
You probably look
like your father!
Or maybe you look
like your mother?
Stop this!
She's a human being!
Are you people making fun
of me for my looks?
Okay, I've got it.
From today on,
you'll be Pesu.
What? My name is Vanessa,
you punk!
Yes, but from today on,
you'll be Vanessa, aka Pesu.
Just Vanessa is fine with me!
Couldn't you just come
with us for now?
Enough of this!
We're supposed to be looking
for an alien octopus!
Alien octopus?
Hold on.
Have you seen one around?
Now that you mention it,
a girl who works here said
that a stray octopus alien
was caught by the Humane Society
and taken away.
‐That looks like...
‐Let's go, Shinpachi!
‐Kagura!
‐Right.
See ya, Pesu look a like.
I said my name is Vanessa!
Gintoki, step on it
or we won't catch up.
Its fine!
In my opinion, it's more fun
to chase than be chased.
That's how young girls grow up to be
adults, by enjoying the chase!
There it is!
Let's go!
‐Whoa!
‐Hey, wait!
Dude it's just a squid.
Listen, this is just like going after a
delicate young girl with a broken heart.
We mustn't chase
after it too far.
The heart of a teen that runs away
from home is also a delicate one.
Adults don't understand
anything about adolescents.
Okay, Gintoki after all
the searching we did,
we've come back
to the octopus jars?
You know, octopuses like
being in jars.
Normally, you have to die
before they can put you in a jar.
You're talking about urns
for ashes.
Listen, Gin, wasn't I trying to tell you
about this idea from the beginning?
It's just a tad different,
I'd say.
If searching around doesn't work,
we'll just wait here patiently.
You just got tired
of searching, really?
Even after the three of us
running around all over the place,
you really think that
this is going to work?
It'll work out.
Well...
you know what?
It's okay.
It'll work out in the end.
Do you know the meaning
of the word responsibility?
This is exactly why guys like
you always end up getting dumped.
I think you're wrong about that.
Give them some sweet talk,
and any woman or octopus
will come wagging their tail.
Women don't have tails.
Neither do octopuses.
You were the one
who said that!
I don't believe it!
He really fell for it!
And who might you be?
Vanessa?
No, it's not!
It's Pesu. Pesu!
‐Pesu?
Get him!
‐No, wait, stop!
Hey, stop squirming!
We're not some
teenage fan girls
scorned by her boyfriend
and treated gently
by another man, you know!
But In that case, the second guy
has all the advantages
of the first guys mistakes!
In this case, our priority is
to chase after Pesu, you guys!
What are we going to do?
‐We can't get out!
‐Fine then!
We just have to roll!
Whoa, this is totally déjà vu!
Holy cow!
Pesu is fast!
‐We'll never catch him like this!
‐Idiots!
Once your feelings start to run
downhill, there's no stopping them.
If we don't catch him you got to date
some rich old hag, Shinpachi!
Married women are hot, too!
How is any of this
all my fault?
Look out!
He's flat as a pancake!
Chill out and help me
find a time machine, okay?
You need to chill out!
And that again?
Seriously?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here's what you asked for.
Pesu!
That thing looks completely dead!
I said unharmed!
Its face is totally discolored!
It's all right.
Girls of this age tends
to use too much makeup.
It happens a lot
during adolescence.
All we did was flatten it with
a jar and it turned out like this.
What a total weakling!
You piflattened it with a jar?
You did this on purpose?
Listen, it's not dead yet, man!
It's just barely alive.
"Just barely alive"
is the problem!
Leaving aside the fact
that it isn't unharmed,
we should be thankful that
it didn't cause too much damage
while it was wandering
around in the city.
Too much damage?
What do you mean by that?
The seas on the planet where
that thing came from are very warm.
Pouring hot water on it will return
Pesu to its original size and state.
Hot water?
Stop!
What do you think
you are you doing?
Boiled octopus!
What are you thinking, girl?
Enjoying it in a delicious manner
is the best memorial service!
Oh, it's coming along perfectly.
What... what did you do,
you idiot?
Pesu?!
No way!
Didn't you hear what he just said
about the water?
Oh, my Pesu!
Pesu's come back to life!
Yeah, I can eat
my fill of octopus!
Well now look.
It's alive again!
As if you had anything
to be proud of!
Whoa! It's pretty strong
for an octopus!
You never told us it would grow
into a giant like that!
I didn't tell you,
because you didn't ask!
Give me a second, and I'll shut
that punk octopus up for good!
Hold on.
Don't you think you've done
enough already?
Don't injure it more
than you already have.
Oh, I remember now!
Is this that creature we saw
going on a rampage on TV?
How're we supposed to capture
something like this?
For that matter, how were you
keeping it as a pet?
Pesu is actually an unknown organism
we discovered on a remote planet.
He became attached to me,
so I tied him to the back of my ship
and brought him home with me as a pet!
Seems like he's not
attached to you anymore!
It must be low on calcium.
Oh, no!
It's headed for the city again!
Hey, Gin!
Come on then.
Kagura, go and buy
some soy sauce.
We're having octopus sashimi
for dinner tonight.
Awesome idea.
Soy sauce, it is!
We're feasting tonight!
No, maybe dumplings
would be better.
It's lunchtime!
Not happening!
What was that for?
Is that my brain leaking out?
Stop trying to hurt it!
The prince told us
to capture it unharmed!
Capture it unharmed!
Unharmed?!
Is that even possible?
That's why I hired you,
Mr. Odd Jobs!
Now make it happen!
Nope, nope,
not happening, nope.
‐Gin, help!
‐Shinpachi!
I'm not letting you
injure that creature!
‐Help! It's going to eat me!
‐You jerk!
I know perfectly well that capturing
that thing unharmed is impossible.
That pinhead prince
won't get the message
until that creature's body
count goes up a bit.
Hello! Are you listening to me?!
So I see you're using
my sidekick as pet food
to get permission
to kill that thing?
It seems like you government guys
really are rotten to the core.
I told you, we have no choice
but to coexist with the Amanto.
Corrupt or not, I'm going to protect
the country the way I see is best.
That's my warrior code.
‐So I see then.
‐Huh?
I'm gonna follow
my warrior code too!
Hold on!
It's one human being
versus a whole nation.
Think about which
is more important!
I don't give a damn about that!
Shinpachi!
Hold on!
Hold on, he says.
Damn it!
I don't really care whether
the government collapses
or the nation falls apart!
Until the day my body
turns to ashes,
I swear that I'm living my life
doing what I think is right!
Gin, I got the soy sauce!
Oh brother, that bastard's messed
everything up!
My precious Pesu!
He's turned into a fountain.
Hasegawa!
What's the meaning of this?
I told you to capture him
and bring him back unharmed!
How will you take
responsibility for this?
It's an intergalactic incident!
Hey, are you listening,
damn it?!
Do what I think is right?
It's almost like the goals
a kid sets in grade school.
Come to think of it,
my mom always used to tell me.
"Screw the rules, my son.
Follow your heart."
And do you honestly
enjoy doing your job?
Mother, am I following
my heart right now?
Hey, Gawa... Hasegawa!
I swear I'm going to tell my father
all about this, Hasegawa!
Shut up.
‐Shut up!
‐Hey!
‐Stop!
‐Shut up you freakin' space flounder!
So, was it the right thing
to do that, you think?
As if I care, moron.
This here is the land
of the samurai.
I'm not going to let them
do what they please.
But you won't be able
to police the Amanto anymore.
You'll be canned
for this for sure.
Boy, you're dumb.
People who act on sheer impulse
always end up ruining their lives.
What?
Gin, will you stop lying around
and get up already?
Take this seriously! It's only been few
episodes since the series started!
With the star of the show like this,
we'll be cancelled before
the end of the season!
The next episode...
By the way, Kagura, what is
that you've been eating?
Octopus dumplings!
Yuck!