Elizabeth!
‐We're having big sales today!
‐Okay now...
I'm going to test your newly
acquired ninja skills...
This place is commonly known
as the Ninja Street.
And we ninja often use it
for training exercises.
Every ninja active in Edo City
learned the art of becoming a shadow
right on this street.
Yeah, but there's nothing here.
It's just an ordinary shopping street.
Oh, so you think you can become
a ninja at a sports gym?
Go die, you four‐eyed bastard!
Hey! Why are you acting
so sadistic only to me?
I see, the best way
to learn how to hide
is to practice in a place
that is filled with people!
Precisely.
So, why are you holding
a plate of curry?
Hey, so what exactly
are we supposed to do here?
Everyone, look over there!
Huh? A bookstore?
Oh, I see.
We must shoplift some books
without being caught...
Listen.
Your test is to go
and buy a porno magazine
without being noticed
by the clerk or the customers.
Say what?
What are you talking about?
What does that have to do
with being a ninja?
This is an actual test,
used even at the
official ninja academy.
Everyone has walked this path
on their journey of growth.
I think you mean
a different kind of growth!
Then, can you do it or not?
You must hide all signs of your presence
completely, and, without being noticed,
instantly pick the type
of porno mag you like.
Then, you have to pay
without the cashier noticing you...
and leave as if nothing happened.
So, can you do it?
Uh... you really like your S&M.
Is this too much of a task
for you guys?
If that's all I have to do, becoming
a ninja won't be very difficult at all.
Watch me.
It'll be a piece of cake.
I mean, a plate of curry.
Hey, you should leave
your curry behind.
You don't need it!
Don't drop the curry,
you'll die if you spill it!
You can do it, Curry Ninja!
I'll curry back!
Curry back!
You mean hurry back,
not curry back!
What's with this obsession
with curry?
He's fast!
Yes, that's quite something.
He's as fast as an actual ninja.
Hey, hey.
He might actually make it.
He... he spilled his curry!
Sorry, captain.
Please take care of the rest!
Curry Ninja!
I told you not to spill the curry!
I'd give him a "B."
He had really good speed,
but he couldn't concentrate at all.
Who's next?
I'll go next then!
And I shall avenge Curry Ninja.
You're not old enough
to buy adult magazines,
so go buy a comic book instead.
Wow! She's like a ninja!
Totally like a ninja!
She's ready and willing.
She loves this kind of stuff!
Wow! She's really enthusiastic!
Come on!
Go ahead and buy it!
Why is she coming back?
What happened?
Is she crying?
Gin...
there was dog poop
on the street.
What do I do?
Captain, don't worry.
I think it's just the curry
that I spilled.
God, it stinks!
Don't try to make me feel better
about lying, Curry Ninja.
Wait, i'll give you
a Curry Ninja "L".
I'll give you an "A,"
so calm down, Kagura!
I don't need a sympathy "A", damn it!
That's it! I don't care about
being the captain anymore.
That's enough.
I guess it's all up to me now.
Believe it or not, I used to play ninja
with my friends all the time as a kid.
Good luck to you, Gin!
Where did Gin go?
That's so cheap!
No it's not, that's a good technique.
It's a special ninja art called
"camouflage in the bin".
I'm so proud of Gin.
He's such a gifted thinker.
‐Why are you going so easy on Gin?
‐You're being completely unfair!
What, you got a problem,
Double Curry?
What's "Double Curry?"
I never even wanted
to wear this suit!
Let me tell you something.
That's not made of yellow cloth.
I made it out of a white curtain
that turned yellow.
So you're a "Yellowed Ninja."
Bastard, get over here!
I'll tear you apart!
Stop, Yellow!
Listen to your captain!
But, Captain!
Why is there even
a garbage bin over here?
Heck if I know.
Well... this is bad, isn't it?
I'm sure it was just
our imagination.
‐No one was actually inside it, right?
‐You're right.
If he was really inside,
he'd be dead by now.
Well... you're up next,
then Shinpachi.
Uh, all right, I'm off then.
‐Say what?
‐Well, uh...
He's quite smooth.
Nobody's noticing him
at all, or rather...
Nobody gives a flying monkey shit
about his existence.
No presence at all...
So then what the heck.
So it doesn't matter whether
you're a ninja or not.
Anybody can pull it off
as long as they're that dull.
‐He really was inside of it...
This is so stupid.
I'm actually glad
I didn't give it a try.
This is just, I mean...
I just went to the restroom
and got beat by a punk.
It's true.
Seriously.
Why are you all looking
at me like that?
Oh, so I see...
Katsura has finally made his move.
It seems that he has gathered a force
to help him free that monster.
They'll most likely attack tonight.
Then he fell for it.
He's exactly like a moth
flying into the flame.
The government's primary enemy,
the Leader of the exclusionist rebels,
Kotaro Katsura.
If I get his head, my position in the
government will be set in stone forever.
I'm counting on you,
Zenzo Hattori.
Let's go...!
We are...
The Mighty Kick‐Ass Power Ninjas!
‐Forward!
You know that they say...
exposing your butt hole in to the moon
light is good for your health.
That's nothing to talk about
while you're on your patrol duty!
I'm being serious.
Usually, the butt hole
isn't exposed to any lights.
Sunlight also works, but apparently
moonlight is even better.
You're saying that just
to deceive me again, aren't you?
I'm being serious.
I heard that Hattori cured
his hemorrhoids that way.
That's enough now!
Katsura could appear somewhere on
the magistrate's property at any minute.
Well, I was trying
to lighten the mood.
Damn it!
I have to pee now!
Hey! Really?
That guy never takes
his duties seriously.
Hey, mister moon!
Please cure my hemorrhoids
with your light!
The moon is coming closer.
Sorry, but listen.
You should go see a doctor
to cure your hemorrhoids.
White Ninja! Special ninja art,
"Chameleon Strike"
It stinks!
Hey, what's all this racket?
‐It's an intruder!
‐Hey, stop you!
The light.
I can't see anything.
Oh, that's not good for you.
You need to put on your glasses.
‐What's this? It stinks!
I can't take them off!
Is this natto?!
Four‐eyed Ninja!
Special ninja Art,
I can't see tomorrow
without my glasses!
Whoa! Oh no!!
Am I gonna be
like this forever?
No way, man!
Ah, but I might like this,
it feels kinda nice...
Right, this may be
a big hit this year,
natto glasses.
‐Hang on!
‐Who are you?
Holstein Ninja!
Special Ninja Art.
"Even though I'm in a Holstein
costume, I still look dull."
Really? With such a beautiful
full moon tonight?
Let's take care of them quick
and have a drink under the moon.
I see. Then how about some
moony‐side‐up curry?!
Red Ninja, Hot!
Yellow Ninja, Mild!
Double Curry Ninja,
Special Ninja Art.
"They're like, Throwing Tons
of Curry Uncontrollably."
Which way to go?
I see, then.
Instead of carrying out
their plan secretly,
their plan is to put
everything into chaos.
It's a very good plan for amateurs.
But it won't work
for professionals like us...
‐...the Real life ninjas.
‐Damn it!
‐Find them!
‐Where did they go?
‐Has anyone seem them?
‐They were right here.
‐We've got to find them.
Gin! Can you move over more?!
My shoulder is sticking out!
It'll get attacked!
‐As for me, I'm completely uncovered!
‐They'll get my shoulder!!
They'll get all of me!
Get out, you guys!
This is for one person only.
I built this by myself, for myself.
Why did you make a brick wall?!
This isn't New York!
If you're complaining, get out!
I'd be happy to hide anywhere,
even in a sewage canal,
as long as I'm with Gin.
Shut up.
There's no space for you either.
What the hell is that stench?!
Don't come near me!
I love it when you talk dirty.
That's what keeps me going!
You really stink!
You smell like natto!
‐Your fingers!
‐Huh? Where's Yellow Curry Ninja?
Hey, what are you doing, Cobra?
My name is not Cobra.
I'm a pine tree!
Idiot! That will never work!
You're completely exposed!
Gin, look over there!
Elizabeth!
Cobra, wait!
Ah, it's the intruder!!
Stop!
Hey, look!
This wall is strange!
‐It's like New York here!
‐Hey!
Cobra! What the hell
are you doing?!
White Ninja!
Everyone!
Are you guys coming with me?
Yeah! They found us
because of you!
I should kill you!
My curry is going to spill!
And then I'm going to die!
Forget about your curry,
just get rid of them!
This is bad.
If we don't do something,
we'll all end up dead.
Sacchan look, don't you have
any useful weapons?
Just leave it to me!
This will slow them down!
Cal... Cal... Trip!!!!
Damn it! We can't get
any closer with these.
Wow!! You formed a perfect
barrier with those!
It is just as I planned.
The Ninja Caltrop Circle.
My ass! There's one stuck
in your forehead!
‐Take that!
‐Die!
You idiots! That is definitely
not how Caltrops
are supposed to be used
last time I checked!
Magistrate!!
They're breaking through the mechanical
traps, one after another!
At this rate,
they'll be here soon!
Do not fret.
They're yet to arrive
to the final room.
What is this room?
Hey! That's...!
Elizabeth!
No! Don't get any closer!
E‐Elizabeth...
Tough luck kid.
Your dear Elizabeth
isn't here anymore.
And you are?
Long time no see,
Ayame Sarutobi.
Oh, Zenzo?
Sacchan, what?
You know this guy?
He's a former Spy Agent
of the government.
Zenzo Hattori.
His unparalleled ninja techniques
made him the most feared
among all of the government agents.
I've been working for the boss
here as a free agent.
It's nothing personal, but if you're going
to side with those fools...
I won't show you any mercy.
I hear you're calling yourselves
the Power‐Ninjas or something,
but an amateur ninja will never
be able to beat a real ninja,
even if you're samurai.
Because we are
the strongest five ninjas.
I am Goh the Goliath!
I am Arnold Swords‐maker!
I am Rose, the Queen of Thorns!
Spam, the Human Calculator!
The God of War, Zenzo Hattori.
We five are...
‐Free‐Agent Ninja Squad.
‐The Shinobi Five!
Katsura and your Power‐Ninjas.
It's game over for all of you!
All members of the Shinobi Five
used to work for
the government's Spy Agency.
And they're all very good,
so you're going to die,
before your beloved Elizabeth.
Elizabeth!
Gin!
Where do you think
you're trying to go?
Comic Samurai!
Oh Gin!!!
I never thought I would meet you
again in a place like this.
Every time I read comics, your face pops
up in my mind, and it's so annoying!
Wait, wait...
Let's see, comic... comic... comic.
Oh, I've got it!
Are you Carl?
I borrowed your comics
but never returned them!
Wait, let me explain myself.
I told you, I'm Hattori.
Hey, you! What?!
Don't tell me you forgot about me!
So, you are Carl,
then, am I right?
I'm Ha‐tto‐ri!
I'm sorry, but I'm not exactly
talented at remembering
the face of middle aged men!
If that's the case,
I don't remember you either!
I don't even know who you are!
Then... why are we even fighting?
Shut up!
I don't remember you
but you're getting on my nerves!
Oh, Gin, be careful!
That man is really dangerous.
You're the one
who needs to be careful.
Bravo then! The way you move
is just like a true simian.
Oh I'm sorry, dear, I didn't know
I was supposed to call you Sacchan,
my little monkey?
Aren't you the ninja academy's
little idol, Horny Rose?
I'm very sorry, I didn't recognize you
under all the makeup!
I never thought Katsura
would be such a weakling.
And the other two are just kids.
According to my data sources,
our chance of winning is 99.8%.
What do we do?
I don't think I can win
against the real ninja.
Hurry! Ready!
Curry? No way!
What kind of a weapon is that?
You expect me to have
curry plates, too?
Whoa!! They've got them too!
Is anyone else seeing this?
I feel like I'm taking crazy pills!
Unfortunately, we have already
calculated your chances of success.
If you strike us with curry, there's 99.8%
of a chance of being blocked.
Shut up! We won't know that
until we try!
Don't underestimate our Triple Curry!
Triple?
Does that include me?
Am I a member of the triple?
We'll show you the difference
between fake and real ninjas!
It's scalding!
A hot piece of potato went down my back!
A hot potato is dancing on my back!
It's hot!
We used the same technique,
but have different results.
This is the difference in our skills!
They're eating it!
Good grief.
Our technique was completely
read by them beforehand!
You're more naive than I thought!
You are the ones who are naive.
What do you...?
‐My stomach.
You bastard, what did you do
to that curry?!
Didn't your mommy tell you never
to take food from a stranger?
You dug your own graves by showing off
your fancy curry technique.
You need to learn some
common sense before being a ninja.
Yeah, you too.
Captain!
What happened?
You, how could you?
I was a little hungry,
so I had a bite of curry!
What? You ate it, too?!
It's fine.
I can overcome this great urge
to poop, I know I can.
Being a ninja is all about
how much you can endure.
Always keep that in mind.
I'll show you
my true ninja technique!
Ninja Art, "Shadow Clone Technique"!
You'll never figure out
which is the real me!
You make it so obvious!!
Oh, no!
Poor Goh really had to go.
Well then, looks like
it's my turn now.
Ninja Art, "Oil Injection!"
Time to get swole!
No‐one asked you
to get swole in your pants!
This isn't good.
According to my data sources,
there's a 99.8% probability
I'll be beaten in the next scene.
It's this scene!
What the hell are you guys
doing down there?
Hattori!
What's the meaning of this?
I thought you guys were the five
greatest ninjas in the world!!
You've got it all wrong.
The Pegasus Meteor Attack
is supposed to be like this.
Idiot, it's supposed to look
like the Pegasus constellation.
Hattori!
What the hell are you
doing down there?
Is this recess in kindergarten or what?
Magistrate!
The Pegasus Meteor Attack!
It's like this, right?
Magistrate!
Give him a big "no" sign!
He's an idiot!
Idiot!
Both of you are idiots!
That technique is done like this!
I recorded all the episodes, you morrons!
Just so you know, you may have been
popular with a small handful of boys
at school, but they were
all disgusting weren't they?
They just had a thing for glasses.
Hey Rose, you know your so‐called
best friend Violet.
She was actually talking crap
about you behind your back.
And you girls!
Would you just stop fighting
like high school teenagers?!
Hey, Gin!
We've got to end this quickly!
Or else Kagura's will be in worst scene
a heroine could ever do!
That doesn't really
get me motivated at all!
I don't really care about Elizabeth or
whether Kagura poops in her pants.
Just wait.
I'll poop in your face
when I get better!
You just wait.
Captain, you gotta relax!
Take deep breaths like me.
Stop! Are you trying
to give birth right now?!
It's getting noisy in here.
Let's put an end
to this fighting already.
I couldn't agree more.
You and I have a lot to talk about.
I wish we'd met under
different circumstances.
Oh, yeah, is that so?
Haven't I been telling you
that we already.
Have met under
different circumstances?!!
He disappeared?
Gin! Look out, Gin!
Below me?
That little rat...
Wait, what's this sweet scent?
I can't move my body!
How do my roses smell?
Ninja Art, "Coiling Aroma Attack!"
Anyone who inhales the scent of my
poison rose will be totally paralyzed!
Now, Zenzo!
Finish him now!
Rin, Pyoh, Toh, Sha,
Kai, Jin, Retsu...
Monkey! How can she move?!
My technique didn't work on her?
Don't tell me she used the smell of natto
to cancel out the scent of my roses?!
Ninja Art!
I will Natto give up!
Wake up now, Gin!
Now, die, Comic Samurai!
The one to die... is you!
Zenzo!
Oh, you're so mean!
Zenzo has hemorrhoids!
And it stinks!
Th‐This can't be...
The Ninja Five.
No way this can happen.
I hope that you make it
in time, Kagura.
Eli... Elizabeth!
Oh, my goodness!
Elizabeth! It's terrible,
absolutely terrible!
Oh, no, this is awful!
Hey, Cobra, isn't that kinda weird?
It looks like some cotton
is coming out.
That's right, and there's
no blood at all, either.
I already told you fools.
Elizabeth isn't here anymore.
Elizabeth was never here
in the first place!
You still don't you get it,
do you, Katsura?
That old man made an
Elizabeth doll to lure you here,
and it worked even better
than we thought.
You guys were completely duped.
Cobra.
Hey, Cobra.
What's the meaning of this?
Come to think of it.
I forgot that we had a fight yesterday
over who'd get fried tofu
in our soba noodle.
So Elizabeth just left the house
because you two fought?!
Gimme a break!!
You made us go through
all this trouble for nothing?
Hello!
I have something to ask you.
Elizabeth, I've been looking
all over for you.
What were you doing?
What's that?
Is it a newspaper salesman again?
Just tell them "to screw off."
I swear they never give up.
Who the hell has money
for newspapers?
Anyway, I'll be coming
home late tonight.
Just microwave one of the hamburgers
in the fridge for dinner I guess.
Ehh... frozen food again?
I'm so sick of it.
It's just not fair.
I know you always go out to eat
good food with random guys
after you cake on
your makeup every night.
Now look what you've done!
You made your father very upset!
You shouldn't say things like that.
Elizabeth, where are you?
Elizabeth!
Hey, Sadaharu!
How did you get so big?
The next episode...