Uh, to all you
boys and girls,
turn on the light
and sit up straight
when you're watching.
Be careful not to become
an adult like me or else.
That's all.
How's the time?
Uh, he should be
arriving very soon, sir.
He's very late.
I swear, Sakamoto had better
not be planning
to stand us up or else.
Katsura, sir!
There!
Looks like he's here.
Sakamoto is not with you?
Well, he's wandered off
like he always does.
He's one very troublesome boss.
Oh, of course.
And so then,
why did you call us out
to a place like this?
I brought you out here
because of this.
It's some kind of present
from our boss.
And Katsura, it's addressed to you.
To me?
Th... this is...
No way!
No way, you can't drop
your load here!
Your excrement is enormous!
It's bigger than the dreams
of a little kid, damn it!
There's no way!
Damn!
This is why I didn't want
to walk you!
She said: "I promise
to take care of him,"
but in the end
it's always the mother
who winds up taking care
of the dog every single time!
Hold on...
am I the Mom now?
You can't even train a pet,
can you, Gintoki?
How pitiful, if you can't
handle just one animal,
how do you intend to move
an entire nation?
And you dare to call
yourself a samurai?
Cobra!
What is that thing?
It's disgusting!
It's not disgusting.
It is Elizabeth.
Yeah, it wouldn't be so bad
if it was on its own,
but the sight of it standing right
next to you gives me the creeps.
Primarily because of you.
That idiot Sakamoto dropped
by my place the other day
and left it behind.
He probably picked it up on
some foreign planet he visited.
It seems like he's gotten
himself totally caught up
with space travel as always.
Hey man, aren't you supposed
to hate all kinds of aliens?
How could anyone possibly hate
an innocent creature like this?
And besides...
she's kind of cute,
don't you think?
Okay, let's go, Elizabeth.
Why don't we go
check out the riverbank?
Cobra, what the heck are you...?
Hey, I told you
not to do that!
Oh, holy crap!
It's huge!
And this smells like hell!
Good grief.
Wow, Katsura of all people?
I'd never have expected
that from him.
Yeah, well, I guess he's sort of
mellowed out these days.
I wonder if he would
take ours, too.
We don't need a roommate
who doesn't contribute anyway.
The only things he contributes
to this house
is feces and suffering!
That's not very nice of you
to say to Sadaharu!
Sadaharu, go ahead
and tear him a new one.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
All right, I'm sorry.
Feces, suffering,
and also urine!
Okay, Sadaharu,
you can let him go now.
Let him go?
He didn't add anything
positive to that list!
Either way, pets are supposed to
be there to provide stress relief.
You shouldn't expect any other
compensation from them.
Hello everyone, we're looking
for unusual pets for our show!
Ever since our country
opened up to the galaxy,
many different animals have
arrived with the Amanto.
Is there a strange pet living in your
neighborhood?
We'll be gathering all of the strangest
and cutest pets in Japan
on our show to crown one of them
the greatest pet of them all!
The winner will receive
a fabulous grand prize.
Stress relief or a
fabulous prize?
Which would you rather have?
You want one week?
Yeah, for sure.
If you wait a week,
I'll pay you the money
gift wrapped, so don't worry.
I already feel like
an oil tycoon!
I'm gonna have all the pickled
seaweed I want!
Those are some pretty small
ambitions for an oil tycoon.
You three sure seem confident.
Well, do you have
some sort of a plan?
‐I do.
‐Unusual for him!
Sort of unusual for us.
I'm getting the feeling that
this plan is something fishy.
Ms Otose, you must not trust
what these guys say.
It's all just big talk!
You know it's all B. S.!
Because it always is.
Hey, you!
What are you doing
back here
as though nothing
ever happened, huh?
Aren't you supposed to be
behind bars right now?
Catherine was released
from prison on bail recently.
She had nowhere else to go,
so she came back here,
and I let her in.
You sure are an
eccentric old lady,
hiring this thief who ran off
with all of your shop's money.
Are you trying to reform her
or something?
It's nothing like that.
I just needed the help
in the shop.
Well, It's your store.
You can steal from others
but not from me,
you cat eared alien!
You don't even have
anything worth stealing,
you bird brained alien
who eats all day!
Be careful of what you say,
you old alien hag!
Want me to let some fish
rot in your mailbox?
If you don't wind up
eating it first,
you bottomless fat ass alien!
She has a point.
Well, you've all had the chance
to meet Catherine, then...
I'll wait one week.
If you don't pay me by then...
well, I shouldn't need
to tell you the rest.
Okay, Elizabeth, shall we go
and visit the park today?
Alright, let's go now.
Come on, bring it!
That's right, come on!
Whenever you're ready!
Okay, Sadaharu,
you just do your best.
Okay, go on, Sadaharu!
Sadaharu!
Right paw!
The left paw!
Sadaharu, sit now!
Hey, we can do this!
He's getting so much better!
Uh, could you tell him...
to be a little bit more gentle
before we get killed
during all this training?
He's right, Kagura.
We're risking our lives to teach him
the most basic of tricks.
What are you three doing?
Oh, it's you, Cobra.
My name is Katsura,
not Cobra.
But more importantly, I asked you
what you're doing here.
Can't you see,
or are you blind?
We're teaching Sadaharu
some brand new tricks.
Oh, is that so?
So you had a change of heart
and decided to take my advice?
Is that what happened,
Gintoki?
Don't be an idiot!
Who would ever have
a change of heart
just because of something
you said?
No, Sadaharu's going to be
on television.
Television?
That's why we're doing
some special training.
Not that it would concern anybody
with a bounty on their head.
Okay, now stand, Sadaharu!
Television.
Don't worry about
being strange!
Being strange just means
that you're more original!
Welcome to our 7th Annual
Weird Cosmic Pet Grand Prix!
I am home!
Hi, welcome back.
How did it go, Ms Otose?
Not good.
They all ran off again.
They run away every time
I go to collect the rent.
If I ever catch them,
I'll beat the living
daylights outta them.
Nothing you say is going to work
with people like that.
One rotten apple
spoils the batch.
The best thing to do is chase them
out before they ruin everything.
It's funny you should say that,
especially considering that you were
just released from prison.
Well, that was that,
and this is this.
You've sure got some nerve,
don't you, girl?
What?
Ms Otose, Ms Otose!
Look there, look there!
Shut the hell up!
Do you want to get thrown back
into a cell again?
No, look there,
look there, at the TV!
From Kabukicho, Shinjuku,
a space creature named Sadaharu
and his owners,
the Sakata family.
The Sakata family, is it?
What the hell are those
morons up to now?
This must be what
they were talking about
when they said
that they had a plan.
The team that gets past
the preliminary round
will earn the right to face
our previous champion,
the Masked Mu family and
their pet, Miss Garter Belt!
Good luck, everyone!
Bring it on, challengers!
I can't believe
we're actually doing this.
Remember that
we're playing to win.
Better get pumped up!
Uh, so... is Sadaharu
the thing that's clamped
onto you and won't let go?
Tell me Mr. Sakata,
are you all right?
I'm just fine.
Sadaharu is a very bright pup,
and he knows
how to hold back.
But it looks like
you're bleeding, sir.
Gintoki, the judges
are getting worried.
Stop the bleeding quickly!
Kagura, hurry up
and stop Sadaharu!
He won't listen to
anybody but you, Kagura.
Great!
Sadaharu, stop,
or you get no dinner
for tonight!
Do you want me to take
away your dinner, too?
Come on and
pull yourselves together!
There's no way we will make it
into the finals like this!
You think?
The judges can't seem
to take their eyes off of me.
Of course they can't take
their eyes off of you!
Go look at yourself
in a mirror!
But you both are just so stiff!
We need to use
the entirety of this stage!
Move your bodies
a little more!
You're the one
that's as stiff as a rock!
Uh, it seems like the owners
are more unusual than their pet.
I think we should cut
to a commercial break.
Alright, let's welcome
our next contestants.
Our next unusual pet today is...
the space creature Elizabeth,
and her owner,
the Space Captain Katsura!
What in the hell is he up to?
Unbelievable!
A wanted man disguising himself
just to get on television.
Well, I guess he really
loves his pet, then.
He likes his pet, alright,
but I think he just likes
wearing that costume.
So Katsura, tell us all.
What exactly is a Space Captain?
Of course, it is a captain,
but in space.
So you'll be facing
Sadaharu over there,
and the winner will be
advancing to the final round.
How confident are you?
That is just a regular
oversized dog.
My dog Taro back home
is about the same size.
What was that, Cobra?
Well, something like that penguin
monster of yours comes out of
the faucet whenever I turn it
on back at my place, too!
Could you not make up
such transparent lies!
It's time to appeal
to our judges!
Come on everyone
and give it up for them.
It's time for the first round.
Go ahead and show the judges
your pet's most attractive features!
As we always mention,
the judges will assign scores
according to their own
arbitrary judgment.
All right, let's begin
with the Sakata family.
This is your time to shine,
the stage is yours!
Sadaharu!
Let's show them the results
of your special training!
Oh, she's damn right we will.
We can't let all the blood we spilled
this past week go to waste.
Can we, Shinpachi?
I think spilled is
a big understatement.
Are you both ready for this?
Gintoki? Shinpachi?
Are you ready, Sadaharu?
It's okay.
Remember, just believe
in yourself.
Mommy knows that you're actually
incredibly talented, okay?
Gintoki, who are you talking to?
Okay, Sadaharu!
Let's go!
Sadaharu, right paw!
Now the left paw!
And for the final trick,
sit down!
Yes, that was just perfect!
It's no different than
the last time we saw this trick!
As if brute force and blood
are all it takes
to call something a trick.
My Elizabeth doesn't perform
such tasteless tricks as these.
Now, it's Elizabeth's time
to appeal to our judges.
It's all yours!
And now watch this!
Paper and paintbrushes?
What is she going
to do with... huh?
Now, show them
what you can do, Elizabeth!
Oh, Elizabeth's painting.
She's painting like crazy
all of a sudden, look!
Whoa!
What's that?
It's a peculiar
but spectacular painting!
It's as though a human being
had painted it!
Hey, announcer, what kind
of description is that?
You're being incredibly rude
to Elizabeth!
Uh... oh, yes, my bad.
I could paint way better
than that garbage painting!
No, that's not the point, Kagura.
Hey, it's all right, guys.
We win when it comes
to leaving a strong impact.
Don't worry about it at all.
The only winning quality
is blood spilled.
This is very fine work here.
I think this talent will achieve
quite a high score.
All right, judges, let's see
your scores for the first round.
Oh my God!
We've got quite a gap in points
straight from the very get go!
Will it be possible to turn
the tables of this contest?
Yeah... that's honestly
what I'd like to know.
This match is over.
Well, everyone, now it is time
to move on to round two.
I will toss
this fried chicken bone,
and the first pet that fetches
this bone back to its master
will be the winner of
this round of the game.
If you win this event,
you will receive 30,000 points
and win the game!
Hey, announcer!
Then what the hell was
the purpose of the first round?
Well, as a show, we needed
to build up the anticipation first.
Said who?
This is idiotic!
I demand you change
the rules right now!
Hey man, Cobra.
Would you quit whining at
the producers and play the game!
If you've got a problem,
then just go home!
What's that?
Now, now, this event
is going to determine the winner.
I wish the both of you
the best of luck.
Why don't we just skip
the boring ass contest,
and just duke it out
like real men?
I was hoping
that you'd say that!
No, this isn't your fight!
Cut it out, both of you,
damn you!
Hey, maybe we can win
this game, after all!
Elizabeth looks like
she's pretty slow on her feet,
doesn't she, Kagura?
Why don't you just
go home?
Okay, here we go,
everyone!
On your mark...
get set...
and.....
Go!
What do we have here?
You Idiot!
No, no, no!
No, come on!
It's over there, you idiot!
Sadaharu is starting
in the wrong direction
and is chasing
after his owner!
Stop, idiot!
I'm telling you,
it's the other way!
What's this?
Mr. Sakata charged
into the judges' table!
Hey stop that, you two!
Please don't destroy
the game show set!
Now, as for the unusual Elizabeth...
What speed!
Elizabeth was thought to be at
a disadvantage at first glance,
but she's running
at breakneck speed!
Are my eyes playing
tricks on me?
For an instant, I thought I saw what
looked like an old dude's leg.
There it is again!
It's a dude!
Enough with your false accusations!
Elizabeth trained very hard
just for today's game.
Don't call her an old dude.
Do you understand?
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Gintoki!
If you're going to run anyway,
just run toward the bone!
Hey, Kagura, you have
to call Sadaharu back!
Who are you talking to?
Don't come this way!
Stop, you stupid dog!
Look out!
Get out of the way!
I'm not moving
from this chair
as the owner of the Annual Weird
Cosmic Pet Grand Prix champion.
I can't just run away from you!
I'll take you on!
Miss Garter Belt,
execute Plan C!
Oh, wow!
Our champion seems
to have been defeated.
How are we going
to hold our final round?
Sadaharu seems to have finally
caught and pinned down Mr. Sakata!
What on earth is your
relationship, anyway?!
Hey, Gin, what will we do?
We're about to lose!
Sadaharu, it's time
for you to move.
Hey, look what I have!
Do you want
this piece of crap?
Come on, come on,
put me down, you damn brat!
And go!
Go?
It appears Mr. Sakata
is using himself as bait
to lure Sadaharu
to the bone!
Sadaharu is charging,
he's like a rhino!
But Elizabeth is already
reaching for the bone.
She's almost there!
There is no way in hell
I'm letting you have the prize.
You let go of Elizabeth
right now, Gintoki!
The prize belongs to me
and Elizabeth, you hear me?
Well, after everything
is said and done,
I guess you still
love your master.
But bite me any harder,
and I'll snap his neck.
So, what are you gonna do?
He's not gonna do anything!
He doesn't understand you!
You bastards, stop changing
the format of the contest!
We can't broadcast this if
you don't follow the rules!
Come on, man.
To hell with
your damn broadcast!
Oh, just screw it.
I'm sick of this crap.
I'm going home.
Can you just get off me?
Oh my God!
What on earth is going on?
That can't be.
Elizabeth...
What the hell was that?
What happened to Elizabeth?
Hey, Elizabeth!
Until just a while ago, I was
headed up the highway to success
but I did that thing on a whim,
and I lost everything.
On the next episode...
All I have now are my sunglasses.