Who is there?
Cobra, still on the run
from the government, huh?
My name is Katsura,
not Cobra.
What are you doing
here anyway?
I heard you escaped from
the government's pursuit
and were laying low
in Kyoto.
I couldn't resist
returning after hearing
there was a festival
going on, so here I am.
Better keep that love of festivals
of yours under control.
The Government hates you
even more than they hate me.
You'll get yourself killed.
There is no way in hell
I would miss a festival
that the Shogun himself
is going to attend, Cobra.
And how do you know
that he will be there?
You're not gonna...?
I don't intend to do
anything that outrageous,
but that sure sounds
exciting, doesn't it?
But of course, if the Shogun's head
were to fly during the festival,
the Shogun Government
and this entire country
would lose their shit.
Hey, you old geezer!
Hiraga, you bastard,
get out here right now!
Do you have any idea
how much trouble
you've caused everyone in
this neighborhood, do you?
The sound of machinery and
clanging metal day and night!
Are you some kind of
Robot Warrior or something?
I don't give a damn if you're
the top inventor in Edo City!
You build nothing but junk.
The Kabukicho Neighborhood
Association has had it with you!
All right, you three.
You can go in and get him!
First up, from Kabukicho
Neighborhood, it's Shinpachi Shimura!
Your father is Bleep Bleep!
What?
♪Your father is Bleep Bleep!♪
Good lord!
I said for you
to stop the noise!
What is this?
You're making it worse!
The two God awful noises
are actually starting
to harmonize together!
The best way to handle a bully
is to bully him right back,
don't you know?
A guy who's never been punched
doesn't understand the pain
and suffering of others.
You're the one
who doesn't understand pain!
My eardrums are about
to explode from this!
What are you talking about,
old lady?
Shinpachi is the one
who's really suffering.
He's showing off in public
how he can't sing at all.
Looks to me like
he's having a blast!
Shinpachi, let me sing
the next song.
I bought the latest song by
Luciano Paparazzi with me.
Come on.
Hey, are you even
listening to me?
‐What?!
‐Cut it out! This is my one...
Oh, man.
What are they doing?
This is all wrong.
Hey, I'm the one singing next!
What did you people
come here to do?
Forget it.
If I have to listen
to you guys sing,
I'd rather sing myself!
‐No one wants to hear...
‐Give me that!
...your stinking singing!
‐Just keep quiet, you rotten old hag!
‐How dare you?
How about a duet then,
damn you!
What?
This is Hiraga, then, uh?
‐Stop, stop, stop, stop!
My head is coming off!
I said my head
is coming off, Hiraga!
Stop it, Hiraga!
You idiots!
I am the one called Hiraga.
You brats are making
a terrible racket
right out in front
of my house.
Think about all the trouble that
you're causing in the neighborhood!
You're the troublemaker,
you old geezer!
That incredible racket
you're making
is driving everyone in the
neighborhood clickety clackety crazy!
I don't ever recall making a racket
that went clickety clack!
It's clackety click!
Hiraga, listen, you're not
a young man anymore,
so try to live
in peace and quiet.
You intend to have those wind up toys
look after you in retirement?
Shut up, you old hag!
I don't care how many times
you come in.
I'm not closing up the shop!
Go home!
Hey, Saburo, don't hold back.
Force all of these idiots out!
Affirmative.
Hey, what... what...?
Stop, stop!
Wow, It's a mountain of robots.
Did you actually make
all of these robots, Hiraga?
What do you you guys
think you're doing,
packing up my stuff
without my permission?
Damn it!
Untie these ropes!
‐Hey, go get me some tea.
‐Affirmative.
Saburo!
Why are you working
like their servant?
Come and help me!
Oh, boy, you sure make
truly good stuff, old man.
Can I get one of these helpful
tin cans for myself?
Hot diggity!
Serves you right!
Saburo can understand human
languages to a certain extent.
He responds to people
who use aggressive words
or actions with his
equally aggressive iron fists.
Okay, release me from
these ropes right now!
Hurry up, you bucket of bolts!
Hey, Otose, is that man really
the top inventor in all of Edo City?
Well, that's what I hear.
But to us, it all just looks
like junk, you know.
It's not junk at all!
Creating something is like
materializing your soul
into something that exists
in reality.
These robots and machines
are all my beloved sons.
Your son's tangled up
over there with a delinquent.
‐Nooo!
‐No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
‐Rocket Punch Fire!
‐Stop it, no!
He can't do that!
You're just tearing
his arms off!
That should do it.
There!
You can make as much noise
as you like out here.
Go crazy.
All the noise that I want?
But my robots
are all broken to bits.
What have you bastards done?
Don't worry at all.
Sabu is okay.
‐Affirmative.
‐Don't "Affirmative" me!
It looks different!
You're missing the arms!
Your arms!
What am I going to do?
I won't be able to finish
in time for the festival!
‐Festival?
In three days,
there's going to be a festival
to commemorate
the 20th anniversary
of the country's opening
to the Amanto.
Even the Shogun is going to make
a rare public appearance.
I have direct orders
from the Government
to have my robots
perform at the ceremony.
What am I going to do?
If I don't finish in time,
I'll have to commit harakiri!
Oh yeah, I forgot that I had
some curry simmering at home.
‐Must run.
‐Hey!
Give me back Saburo's arms!
Darn those stupid kids!
They're all crazy.
Are you going to be
all right, Hiraga?
Oh, I've got no choice, do I?
If I work around the clock,
I might...
Not that.
I was talking about your son.
If I'm not mistaken,
wasn't the Shogunate...?
Otose, the trick for an
old man to live a long life
is to quickly forget about
anything he doesn't like.
And I've told you before,
this robot is my son now.
Hey, dad!
Hey, dad, please stop!
What good will making robots
for murdering people do?
Dad, didn't you say that you wanted
robots to help people?
Didn't you say that?
But now it is the time,
the time to change.
If things remain as they are,
this country will be taken over
by the Sky people.
This is the only thing that
I can do to try to stop them now.
Alright, dad, then I'm going
to fight instead.
What are you talking about?
Listen, dad, I noticed that
you stopped smiling a long time ago.
You know, dad...
I loved watching you work,
working happily on your robots
all covered in grease,
looking exactly like a little kid
playing in the mud.
So I have decided.
I don't want
to see you working
with such a grim look
on your face anymore.
Hey, wait up!
Wait, Saburo!
Listen up.
On the day of the festival,
the Shinsengumi will protect
the Shogun
with every last man
in our ranks.
If the Shogun so much as gets
even a single scratch on him,
then the heads of every
last one of us will roll!
I want you to keep
that in mind, alright?
If you see anyone suspicious,
kill them without hesitation!
I'll take full responsibility.
Are you for real, sir?
In this case, I'll start by killing
every samurai in sight.
I appreciate this opportunity.
Okay, guys!
Please just disregard
that last order.
Also, although this intelligence
is still unconfirmed
we have information that someone
really dangerous is in Edo City.
Someone really dangerous?
Who could that be, huh?
Remember that incident where
over a dozen government officials
got assassinated during
a dinner meeting?
Well, that was his work.
The most radical and dangerous man
among all the Exclusionist Rebels.
His name is Shinsuke Takasugi.
‐Let's invite Yo too!
‐Yeah.
This sweet, seductive
smell must be...
cotton candy!
Cotton candy!
Ah, damn!
Quit playing around
and get back to work!
We are very short
on time as it is!
But listen, Hiraga, the festival
has already begun.
I mean, we came
to help you,
but I still don't think
we're going to make it.
The robot performance
doesn't start until tonight.
If we can somehow
finish by this evening,
we'll manage just fine.
Don't try to play
dumb with me!
Look at at this!
You think I wouldn't know
about this shirt having lipstick
all over it?!
Look here, don't think
that you can lie to me anymore!
Tell me exactly
where this came from!
Affirmative.
"Affirmative, affirmative."
That's all you ever say!
That's why your subordinates
all look down on you!
Try saying "no", for a change,
or you'll never be promoted!
Affirmative.
Ah... that's it!
‐Domestic Violence!
‐What are you doing?!
Stop that!
Who is she?!
It's that girl, isn't it?
That ugly, witch who came
to our housewarming party!
Stop it, I said!
What sort of sick soap opera
are you playing at?
It might be playing to you,
but to me, it meant
everything in the world.
You just don't understand!
We somehow managed
to finish on time.
Although there are
a couple kinks left unsorted.
If you guys hadn't shown up,
I wouldn't have had any problems
getting finished at all.
Get off your pedestal,
you aging public hazard!
We only came because
that old hag forced us to.
I still have some
final adjustments to make.
You'll only get in the way,
so go check out
the festival or something.
Gintoki, hurry, hurry!
Thank you, Hiraga!
They sure are a rowdy bunch,
aren't they?
Right, Sabu...?
Saburo!
Hey, you can't go with them!
Saburo, stop!
Wow, let's eat fried udon next!
How odd. It almost looks as
if Saburo is having fun too.
Well, the truth is anything's
more fun than hanging out
with a grim faced
old geezer like you.
Hey, you say the same thing
that my son did.
Wait, your son?
You had a son?
I didn't know that.
I did, but he is gone now.
He went off to war
on his own and he died.
He loved robots every bit
as much as I do.
A brat who would sneak in to tinker
with all of my machines.
When I think back now,
that must have been the happiest
time of my entire life.
Back then I tinkered with robots
because I loved them.
But then ever since people started
calling me the greatest inventor
in Edo City and such,
robots just became
a means to an end.
That son of mine rebelled
against me for that and left me.
And that was it.
And that reminds me...
I heard something.
I heard from Otose that
you also went to war as well.
It's not anything for me
to be proud of.
I lost a lot of friends
during that time.
Don't you ever want
to avenge their deaths?
Haven't you ever thought of
striking back at the Government
and the Amanto for
the friends you've lost?
Old man, you're not thinking....?
Oh, shoot!
I have some final adjustments to make,
so I'm heading back now.
Hey, Saburo, let's go.
Oh, it's that old dude.
Oh no, it's that girl
with the venomous tongue!
Oh, if it isn't Hasegawa!
You finally found a job!
Congratulations!
Oh, thank you!
How are you two doing?
Are you on a date?
A shooting game?
Maybe I'll have a try at it.
Oh, go ahead,
go ahead, go ahead!
It's on me!
If I hit it, will you give me
anything that I want?
Sure, I'll give it to you.
Take good aim and...
‐Hand over your shades.
‐What?
You did it wrong.
You were supposed
to aim that way.
I just won that nice watch.
Now just a minute!
Wait a minute!
Come on!
I said I'd give you anything,
but not my personal property!
Hey! Are you listening?!
I just won the beard.
I scored the jacket.
I'm taking the nipple!
Hijikata, I noticed Okita
hasn't been back at all
since he said that he had
to go take a dump.
That bastard is probably
goofing off again.
Hijikata, you can have
your doubt of anyone else,
but doubting one of our own
is not something I can approve.
I really believe in Okita.
I'm sure he's just having
a hard time getting it all out.
That's what I believe.
I think he'd rather
you just doubted him
if that's what you're going
to be believing of him.
But that damn Yamazaki
sure is late.
What happened?
The Shogun said he wants
to eat octopus dumplings.
He doesn't have a care
in the world.
Hey, Vice‐Chief,
sorry for the delay!
I've returned with your food!
Hey, you're late!
You better not have forgotten
the mayonnaise!
Hey... this looks like...
Forgive me,
I was in such a rush
that I tripped and
they fell out on the way back.
Forgive me, sir.
I, Sagaru Yamazaki,
have made a blunder I regret.
I see, though I think the
bits of food around your mouth
are a blunder you're going
to regret for the rest of your life.
Yamazaki!
Vice‐Chief, this isn't
what you think!
This is from the hot dogs...
‐...I ate along the way!
‐It's too late for excuses!
Hey, what are you
going to do?
You're... you're eating it?
Don't get so upset, Hijikata.
Today is a festival.
I can't help it.
That bastard Takasugi
has no political beliefs at all.
He only enjoys creating chaos.
There's no way
a guy like that
is going to overlook
a huge festival like this!
Oh! It's started. The Show by
Edo City's top robot puppeteer,
Gengai Hiraga!
A festival must be loud
to be interesting, that's for sure.
Don't you move.
To think the man they called
the White Knight
would let someone
take his six.
Gintoki, have you finally
lost your edge?
What are you doing
in a place like this, huh?
Just shut up
and watch, Gintoki.
An incredibly exciting show
is about to begin.
Saburo, let's do it.
Affirmative.
Fire!
It's a terrorist attack!
It's the Exclusionist Rebels!
Is this a smoke screen?
Hey men! Secure the area
around the tower.
Don't let a single rat
near the Shogun!
It's an army of robots!
Looks like the crowd
has made it out.
Okay, start it up!
Men, forward!
Attack!
So tell me,
do you remember, Gintoki,
how there was
that one time when I led
a volunteer army
called the Cavalry?
At that time, there was
a man named Saburo.
He wasn't any good
with the sword,
but man, he was incredibly good
with building machines.
He said he didn't join
to fight a war.
He came to fight
for his father.
His father was
all he ever talked about.
But then he died without ever
being able to return to his father.
What a sad story, right?
I mean we all risked our lives
to protect our country
from the Amanto people,
but our very government
welcomed the Amanto
without a second thought.
Even the Cavalry
was no exception.
We were caught in the purge,
and eventually destroyed.
When he saw
his son's head exposed
for public viewing
by the riverbed,
who knows what
his old man thought.
Takasugi, were you the one
who egged the old man on?
Egg someone on?
Don't be ridiculous.
I saw a pair
of splendid fangs,
so I just polished them
a little bit.
You see, Gintoki,
I understand the suffering
that old man is going through.
There still remains
a dark beast of vengeance
stirring deep down
inside me as well.
Thrashing about all day
and all night,
saying endlessly
in my ear: "Kill.
Kill the enemies
of my friends.
Make them suffer
the way we suffered."
Gintoki, can't you hear
those voices as well?
No, well, I suppose you can't.
Looking away from
your own past
and living a carefree
life these days.
You've lost your fangs
to indifference.
You couldn't understand
how we feel.
Your biggest mistake is
underestimating me, Takasugi.
I've got a beast
of my own too.
It won't move.
But the beast in me
is a white one.
And what is it's name, you ask?
We call him Sadaharu!
No way!
My beloved, glorious
famed blade is...!
Ah, Hijikata, my beloved blade...
‐...is no way!
‐Shut up!
This isn't the time for that!
But I'm still paying off
my loan for this.
‐No way!
‐Damn it.
We keep cutting them down,
but they keep coming back.
There's no end to this.
What was that?!
Who are the bad boys
who are ruining the festival?
Where are you?
That's a phantom called
"The Festival Musical!"
An ancient spirit who punishes
the likes of biker gangs
who interfere with festivals!
I don't really think so.
The God of the festivals
has descended to help us!
Victory is ours!
Next, we will use real bullets,
so aim carefully, Saburo.
Affirmative.
Please stop this right now!
The Shogun is already
long gone from the festival.
Is that so?
Well, my eyes are going bad,
so I couldn't see that.
But that's okay.
Then, I'll just go
after that pesky group
called the Shinsengumi.
Hiraga, stop!
Hey, hey!
That's quite a dangerous show
you're putting on out here.
Is it some sort
of superhero show?
Well then let me play
the hero for today!
You're not good enough
for the role, Gintoki.
Who are you
to diss the actor...
when you wrote
such a crappy script?
Revenge flicks
are so outdated, anyway!
Besides,
you're disappointing Saburo.
Which Saburo do you mean?
Both of them.
Nobody ever wanted things
to turn out like this.
You know that better
than anyone else, Hiraga.
Yes, I do know that.
But I just cant stand
the pain anymore.
Letting my son die like that,
while this old body
continues to live on.
I'm tired of living my life
just staring at useless things.
I actually don't really give a damn
about the Shogun's head anymore.
I fully realize that
there's nothing I can to do
for someone
who's already dead.
All I want at this point is to die,
living by my principles.
So get out of my way.
I'll show you no mercy
if you get in my way.
I'm not moving, because I have my
principles that I live by, too.
Fire!
Saburo!
You idiot!
Why didn't you fire
your weapon?
D... dad...
I loved...
watching you...
work happily...
like a kid...
playing and having...
fun in the mud...
I loved you like that, dad.
What is it with all of you?
What do you
want me to do?
How do you expect me
to go on?
How do I go on living?
What meaning is there
in my life now?
It totally beats me.
Just go on living
a long life, maybe?
It looks like
you failed in your plan.
We had unexpected interference.
I thought he'd lost his fangs
a long time ago,
but, boy, was I wrong
about that!
When it comes to protecting
something important,
everybody bares their fangs.
You, who no longer
has anything to protect
are nothing more
than a beast, Takasugi.
I'm fine being a beast now.
I have nothing to protect,
nor do I need one.
I will simply
destroy everything,
until the beast
inside me stops whining.
Hey, you depraved priest!
My name is Katsura,
and I'm not a depraved priest.
What do you think
you're doing?
Look here, you broke it!
This is a wind up toy?
Hey, stop touching that!
‐Why don't you just buy it already?
‐Oh, wow!
‐Just buy the damn thing...
‐Look at that.
...and I know you'll love it!
He looks like
he's doing alright now.
The Masked Loincloth Bandit?
Who is that?
He wears a red loincloth on his head
and steals pretty girls' underwear
to distribute to all
the unpopular guys!
The next episode...