The land of the samurai.
There was a time,
a long time ago
when our country
was called by that name.
With the arrival of the "Amanto",
or Sky People from outer space
and the Sword Ban
enacted 20 years ago
the samurai class fell into decline.
In these hard times there was one man
left with the spirit of the samurai.
His name is Gintoki Sakata,
a reckless jack of all trades
with a serious sweet tooth
and big heart.
Due to some rather
unexpected events,
I, Shinpachi Shimura,
ended up working with him,
for a while at least.
What is the true nature
of this man's soul?
It's very difficult to tell,
but though dim,
I think it's definitely glistening.
Hey, Gintoki!
It's about time that you pay off
the accumulated rent that you owe me!
Hey, Otose!
The other day I fixed
your VCR, remember?
That oughta be enough
to square us!
Square us?
As if!
That's not even close
to being enough for five months!
And the VCR broke again, so I couldn't
finish watching all the episodes
of "The Ed Sullivan Show!"
You idiot, don't ever give up!
I'm sure they'll air it on TV again!
You'd better just shut your yapping
and pay me the rent that you owe,
you mop headed oaf!
Get off my back!
You don't understand
the suffering
that people with mop tops
have to go through!
As if I care, moron!
‐If you don't have any money to pay me...
‐They're at it again
...then sell one of your kidneys or
your testicles or something!
Sometimes I wonder if it's a good idea
to continue hanging around this man.
‐You're borrowing money from this dirty old hag!
‐Hey come on, stop it, you two.
So then, what does that make you?
Aaaaaagh!
Uh?
‐Hiyeah!
‐Whoa!
"Sometimes" is an understatement.
Inoue, I hear that you've been making
quite a mess of things lately, huh?
Is that so?
I'd go on a real rampage,
but I've been holding back lately,
because there's this annoying bunch
that's always in my face crying.
Listen up, moron.
There is only one thing that's waiting
for the people who don't understand
what it means to show
respect in this world.
Hold back a little.
I'm telling you
for your own sake, man.
I don't think I understand.
Tell me, what exactly are you saying
is waiting for me if I don't hold back?
You'd better know your damn place,
you little tight permed nuisance.
Don't you know what kind of
damn situation you're in right now?
I don't expect some chump
like you with a crew cut
to understand the artistry
of these tight perms.
You clean cut cretin should just
stay on the sidewalks
and stay out of the way,
and then maybe you wouldn't
have to get hurt!
What the hell you said?
You got a problem
with crew cuts, dirtbag?
Master, please, if you will.
Sorry to say.
You are all dead.
Wow, someone really made a mess
of things here, didn't they?
That's true.
I don't really care what happens
to a bunch of crooks like these.
But I do wonder
who did them like that.
Oh, darn it!
Today's the day the new
comic book comes out!
I totally forgot that this week
it comes out earlier than usual!
Should we turn back?
No, forget it, man.
We've already got the groceries
to make our hotpot.
Yeah, you're right,
and this might be a good chance
to give up this crazy habit.
I mean, reading comic books
at my age...
No, but men are always boys
at heart until they die.
I'm sorry, but could you keep your
embarrassing emotional problems to yourself?
‐Hey, look out!
‐Huh?
Oh my God,
you ran her over!
What're we gonna do
about this?
Why weren't you
paying attention to the road?
Don't get so worked up.
Chill out and help me
find a t... time machine.
No, you chill out!
It... it should be okay,
you know?
A fortune teller I saw on TV said
people with my horoscope
would be lucky this weekend.
I'm sure that she is
miraculously unharmed, okay?
Hey there, young lady, hello.
Oh, those freaking psychics!!!
Liars!
I'm never watching
any of their shows again.
Darn it! Why do they always
have to be so convincing?
Hey, how is she doing
back there?
She's not even twitching at all.
Darn it, then we need
to get her to a doctor!
Huh?
Wait, what in the world...?
Huh... ooooh!
Huh?
You guys stupid
or something?
I'm not going to die just from
getting run over by motor scooter!
This scar's from getting shot
by those guys.
‐Already closed up, see?
‐How come?
Did you eat glue with all of
your meals or something?
Whatever.
You seem all right,
so we'll be on our way.
Get well soon!
Huh? Shinpachi, did you suddenly
put on some weight?
How could a grown up
man like you
abandon a girl who's being hunted
by the mafia?
Because I'm still a boy
at heart, ask him.
And besides, in this country
we don't call people strong enough
to stop a scooter
with one hand "girls".
We call them mountain gorillas.
Hey! There they are!
Over here!
Oh, no!
This is bad!
Wait! Who are they?
Are they pedophiles?
What, potato pies?
Stop right there!
Hey, who are you?
And what are you?
What did you do with your super
strength to make them so angry?
I heard that...
I heard that
I could earn some sick cash
if I came to the Capital.
And so traveled all the way to
Edo City from a distant planet.
My family...
well, they're very poor.
Nothing but white rice
for every meal.
I mean, I'd like to at least be able
to eat an egg with my rice.
Well, that's not much better.
But then one day,
the mafia made me an offer.
Care to change your life
by coming with me?
If you do, you can have some soup
with your rice three times a day.
Well, I heard that and
jumped at the opportunity.
Why in the world?
I mean, at least eat something
different for each meal!
The thing is, I'm actually really sturdy
compared to Earthlings.
So of course I took their offer
and I had rice with soup
every single day.
I was so happy.
But recently, their demands
have been "escalator."
Uh, you mean "escalating."
The last assignment
they gave me,
they told me to get
someone's testicle balls.
No, not testicle balls,
just balls is fine.
Just balls.
I don't like being here anymore.
Edo City is very dodgy.
I want to go back home.
Boy, are you dumb, girl?
In this country there are two things
you cannot trust at all,
and that is guys with perms
and girls in red clothing.
No, you got yourself
into that world.
And so, you need
to get yourself out,
so see ya around.
Hey, wait up!
‐I wonder if my comics are still on sale.
‐Oh.
Don't worry, I'm sure
things will work out.
‐Oh!
‐Well, you want to go home, don't you?
So, then I'm going
to help you get home.
You will?
I may not look it,
but I'm a jack of all trades.
So I'm used to dealing
with situations like this.
A jack of all trades?
I'll do absolutely anything
that you ask.
Simply put,
I'm a kind of handyman.
Oh!
If you want to leave Earth, you'll first
have to go to a Sky Terminal.
Right, let's go then!
Are you guys idiots or what?
How can it be so hard
to bring back one girl?
You call yourselves gangsters?
Do you think it's fitting
for my employees?
Do you think it's fitting for someone
with a tight perm like I have?
But bossman, we're up against
a member of the Yato clan.
Even all of us together
are no match for...
Is there anything inside
that skull of yours?
That's why we need her!
If we use that monster girl's
mighty strength,
the tightly permed mob could finally
reach heights never seen before!
Okay, okay, let me go.
Okay, relax guys.
But if she refuses to come back,
I'm finished going easy on her.
You must kill her.
Otherwise, she'll become
a serious threat
if she goes and joins
a different gang.
It's best to get rid of any tools
we're finished using,
or they could get in the way.
Are you ready?
Let's go!
Look! Look there!
There she is!
Over there!
Really?
They found us already?
Gee, you're so useless,
four eyes.
That's why I said
I wanted a helicopter.
Wait, what helicopter?
You were the one
who told me
that we could outsmart them
by staying outside of the alleys!
You better stop running!
Do you have any
of the new comics?
We just sold out earlier.
I see, well, thank you anyways.
Do you finally feel
like using a helicopter?
Well, we don't have
that kind of money.
‐Huh?
‐Oh! It wasn't a joke after all!
Hey, look over here!
Do you have any comic books?
I have the latest issue
of "Youngblood".
The latest issue of "Youngblood"?
It stinks in here!
Now's not the time for that.
You just need to deal with it!
God, this is so bad!
But it stinks!
Oh, comics.
Comics... comics...c...
Comics...
Comics!
Lucky me!
They really are persistent.
So how long do you think
they plan on following us?
Well you tell me.
How did you plan
on helping me,
when you can't even
get us a helicopter to use?
You know it's not that easy.
I don't think I could even
afford an RC helicopter.
Stop making excuses and get us a
helicopter, you good for nothing kid.
You are getting mad at me?
I'm the one helping you out!
How can you be that way?
You're really just getting in the way,
so don't get cocky!
If you don't have money,
then give me some ideas!
What's with that?
Your demands were
the cause of all this! Uh!
What the...?
Where on earth did they go?
There's no way that
they could've gotten far. Uh!
All right, that way!
We managed to get this far.
Any sign of the perm boys
anywhere?
No sign.
We are all good.
If you catch the train from here,
you'll go straight to the Sky Terminal.
Then you'll be able
to go home.
I just can't help but think
about how heartless Gin is
looking for comic books
at a time like this.
It doesn't faze me.
Everyone in the Capital
is like that.
They're cold hearted and
unsympathetic at least towards others.
But that's a very smart
way to live.
Unlike meddling folk who always
stick their noses in...
they're stupid.
And in the end, stupid people just
end up being taken advantage of.
But I think it's much better
to be stupid than be a jerk.
‐Although I really hate you.
‐Huh?
That's weird, it sounded like you
just said something really nasty
with a straight face!
Honestly, I really hate
dorks with glasses.
Hey, what on earth
do you mean by that?
Are you bipolar or something?
What's with all of the insults?
After all that I've done for you!
‐Huh?
‐What's the matter?
I'm totally stuck.
No way... me too.
Oh no!
I want to cry!
The train's leaving!
We don't have a choice.
‐We have to roll!
‐Whoa!
Hey, hey, this isn't good, running into
an oncoming train is dangerous.
This is just too bad
for you, Kagura.
And you were so close
to escaping.
Inoue!
How cold of you to run away
without even saying goodbye to me
and after I treated you so well.
What happened to all
of your money problems?
Don't tell me you're about to go back to a
lifestyle of eating nothing but white rice.
I refuse to make money
off the suffering of others!
I refuse!
Nothing tastes good
when you earn it that way!
Even plain rice tastes good
after a day of hard, honest work!
That's funny coming
from someone
who doesn't know how to do
anything but fight, huh?
Isn't that right, Miss Yato Clan?
Yato Clan?
Oh dear, oh dear.
You've been helping her without
knowing who she really is, huh?
But of course you've heard
of them before, haven't you?
The mightiest and nastiest
of the mercenary races, the Yato.
They don't look all
that different from humans
but they boast
phenomenal strength,
and with it they have destroyed
countless planets.
They're a warrior race
that simply loves to fight.
It seems like you were hiding it, but
the proof is your white translucent skin
and that parasol you carry.
They say the Yato
hate sunlight,
so they always have to carry
their parasol on them.
Hey, Kagura!
You've covered your instincts with a
paper thin layer of morals,
but you were enjoying yourself
when you were fighting.
Deep down you crave blood.
‐This is your true nature, Kagura.
‐You're wrong, though!
Because I have...
I have traveled across the galaxy and came
to Edo City in order to reinvent myself.
I will ask you again, Kagura.
There's this really, really bad guy
who's been picking on us lately.
Is he really a bad guy, Inoue?
Uh‐huh.
I guess I have to fight him.
That's why...
That's why I was so foolish.
Having rice with soup
is the very best!
I believed your words
and you manipulated me.
You used me!
You're useless to me
if you're not gonna fight.
Goodbye, then.
Wait, hold on a second!
Hold on!
Please don't leave us!
Oh, no way!
The set up is right out
of an anime or comic book!
Dreams are like trees.
It's more fun to climb them
than to watch them.
And there are things you only learn
when you climb them.
For example, I sweat a lot.
Fountain pens are
a real pain in the butt!
It's a pain in the butt drawing
backgrounds, too!
Comic books are such a pain
in the butt to draw.
Come to think of it, just living
is a pain in the butt.
I want to become
steamed cheese bread!
Oh, no way!
The set up is right out of
an anime or comic book!
You guys are nothing
but a lot of trouble!
It's Gin!
Hey, the two of you
better clench your teeth!
Huh? Hold on!
Hold on!
Go, you're free!
What?
What happened?
What's going on?
I like to fight.
‐I really like to fight.
‐Huh?
That is the Yato's true nature
and I won't deny it.
But from now on
I want to fight against the Yato
nature that's within me.
And I'm going to kill you,
so I can change!
You... you Yato idiot!
Come on, now, men, right now.
Come and get them!
Alright?
Huh... I can't do this anymore!
‐Get them yourself, you permed moron!
‐Hey, come back here!
‐Inoue!
‐Ye... ye... yes.
How can I help you?
You remember, don't you?
The first thing
you told me that day?
Care to change your life
by coming with me?
Did I really say something?
Inoue, there's something I've been
meaning to say to you.
That afro hairdo just isn't
a good look for you at all!
Hey it's not an afro,
it's a tight perm!
Who cares!
Oh! I hate this.
I found one!
If you were gonna help us,
you should have just come
with us from the beginning.
I don't understand you at all.
Are you shy?
Oh, I didn't exactly come here
to help you out.
I was only looking
for my comics,
and I just happened
to come to the station.
Our lives are worth less than a couple
of dollars and a comic book?
Oh, look, the train's here.
Get on quick and don't come back
here again, nightmare girl!
Well, I'd really like to do that,
but when I think about it,
I don't have any money to pay
the fare for my way home.
So, I'm going to stay here a
little longer and save money.
So with that being said, I'm going
to ask you to let me work for you.
No! You... you've got
to be kidding!
Why would I hire a girl
as violent as you are?
I'm sorry, did you say something?
‐No, ma'am, not a word.
And so, our workplace
got a lot livelier yet again.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go get them.
May I have some extra helpings?
Just how many bowls
do you think you've had?
This isn't a restaurant.
This is a place that serves drinks
along with a helping
of healthy eroticism, not food.
It's a hostess bar,
a haven for old men!
If you just want to eat,
then why don't you go order
a kid's meal at a fast food restaurant!
I have no interest
in fancy food.
Pickles are just fine.
You've sure got simple taste
for such a little pig!
Hey, Gintoki, tell me,
what's with this little girl?
She's already had five
bowls of rice!
Where's she from?
Five bowls, huh?
She's still got a lot more to go.
And all we have left at home
is a little sugar and salt now.
What's with those two?
All skinny and worn away like that.
Huh?
Hey, you're still eating?
Somebody, stop her!
Somebody!
We're mistaken for terrorists and
are chased by the Shinsengumi.
But Gin's friend, Katsura, helps us out.
Hey, Cobra, it's been a while.
The next episode...
Umm... Do you have a copy of Bleach?
We only have Gin Tama.