When watching Gintama,
please keep the lights on
and don't sit
too close to the TV!
‐You can't catch me.
‐Hey there, pops.
Come and get me.
‐So, what's up little Odd Jobs girl?
‐Your turn.
Why are you always here
in the middle of the day
when grown ups
are all working, pops?
That is because...
I was actually fired
from my job.
So what was the reason
that you were fired
from your job, pops?
Well, it's because...
It's because I blindly followed
my heart without thinking ahead.
You should be careful
not to be too reckless in life
just because you're young
too, little girl.
Because life is very long,
you know.
I really don't want to hear that
from a loser like you.
See you,
dumb old repulsive kook!
Aka dork!
Let's go, Sadaharu.
Man, kids these days, huh?
Oh, whoa, that's weird.
Everything's blurry.
I can't see.
If you stop
and think about it,
your life's a lot longer
as an old guy than a kid!
Whoa, Scary!
See you, dumb old
repulsive kook!
Aka dork!
A dork, that name
really fits me,
far better than it should.
Until just a little while ago
I was sprinting down
the path to success.
If only I hadn't made
that one reckless error.
The next day, I was summoned
by my boss.
Cut your guts out.
Seriously?
My boss ordered me
to commit harakiri,
and I was scared.
So I was going leave
everyone behind and bail.
But as it turned out,
my wife left me first.
I can't stand by a dork‐h,
(a dumb old repulsive kook husband)
like you anymore.
I'm sorry, but I'm leaving.
Hatsu.
I lost absolutely
everything in life.
The only thing I had left
were these black sunglasses.
Well, I lost everything,
but I did gain
something else in return.
Yo!
Here again, huh?
How's it going?
You winning at all today?
A very strange acquaintance.
You know, a guy your age
just passing the time
at this place every
single day is as sad
as the ice cream that gets left
on the lid of the container.
And what about you?
Do you also have
nothing better to do
than hang around here
during the day all the time?
Well, when people can't get
enough sugar in their bloodstream,
they start to not know
what to do anymore.
So, when that happens,
watching small balls
popping around like this
makes me feel a lot better.
It's very simple.
It's said that birds
of a feather flock together.
But I really felt like
this guy was just like me,
particularly the way
he didn't have any guarantee
of fulfilling his basic needs.
I feel like I'll win today!
Ah? You're leaving already?
Actually, I've got a job interview
to go to today.
Oh, wow, you're actually
making a serious effort.
Kind of.
See you.
Man, is my lucky streak
already over?
That's right.
I really needed to start something
brand new in my life at this point.
I know that I'm a dork,
but I should at least
become a far better man
than I've been until now.
What the frick?!
Stop surprising me,
old man!
But I'm the one
that was surprised by you.
I was just going
to offer you a light.
Oh, uh... thanks a lot.
I'm just really nervous, man.
It's upside down, man!
I mean, how nervous
can you be?!
Sorry, sorry.
It's the first time I've been
to this kind of place.
My girl is been providing for me
up until this point.
But now, the thing is,
she's pregnant
and uh... she's due
pretty soon.
So, I thought I should
be a man...
and get a real job
to provide for the family!
Hey, hey, it's burning!
It's burning!
Yeah, a flame of responsibility
has been ignited
deep within my heart!
No, not that!
Your head is totally
on fire, man!
Take a look!
Oh... oh, my God!
What do I do?
Water! Water! Water!
Mr. Shoji Endo, it's time
for your interview.
Damn you're fired up!
Look, my wife is taking care
of the housework!
From now on, I've decided
I'll earn money for my family!
You're fired uuuup!
Oh, hey!
Compared to this guy,
my responsibilities
as a dork are small.
I'm Taizo Hasegawa.
It's very good to meet you.
Hasegawa?
Mr. Hasegawa, is that you?!
You... you are from the Department
of Immigration Control?
I'm Onishi!
I never thought I'd see you
in a place like this!
So, what are you doing here,
Mr. Hasegawa?
Well, I've had a lot
of problems recently,
but I'm glad to know that
you're working for this company
and I wonder if you can
put in a good word for me
with your boss
for old time's...
Are you freaking kidding me?!
O... Onishi?
You're a bastard, Hasegawa!
Thanks for everything
you did for me
while I was working at the Department
of Immigration Control!
Hey, I didn't have any choice at
the time, because of my boss.
You shut up!
If you want to work here,
you'd better bow down before me
and shave off
that stupid goatee, buddy!
Shave my goatee?
You got a problem with that?
And take off those shades
while you're at it, batbrains!
No, anything but my sunglasses!
You don't have a job, but you still
want to have a style, huh?
You know what you are?
A dumb old repulsive kooky geek,
aka you're a dork‐g!
Now get out!!!
Everything has been going
utterly wrong since then.
Can you do something
about your hair
and those stupid sunglasses?
They make you look
like a dork!
And I mean, a drowsy
old repulsive kook.
It's just, your breath stinks
and your sunglasses are kind of...
You're a degraded
old repulsive kook,
in other words, a dork!
No matter where I go,
I hear the words dork.
Hey, there, chef!
What's this disgusting overcooked
rotten kefir flavored stock?!
In short, it is dorks!
What's wrong with
being a dork?!
Times like these call
for a drink or ten.
You know, the area
around my heart
has been hurting like
it's being stabbed recently.
Is this what they call
love sickness?
You should probably
see a doctor, Mr. Mu.
Get home safely.
Oh, welcome.
Good evening.
Hey, we're about
to close up.
It's time for you to leave.
Can't you let me drink
a little bit more?
I'm trying to bury the harsh
realities that weigh heavily
on my stomach in the
bottom of these bottles.
Just make sure
you don't spill all the food
that's weighting heavily on your
stomach across the bar counter.
Come on, take off your sunglasses
and wake up.
Leave me alone.
I'm just fine, I'm fine!
Are you serious, man?
You're a drunk old recovering
knocked down customer.
In short, a dork‐c.
Come on, fellows,
check it out!
Whatever, I don't care, dork.
Check it out!
Hey, brother!
I know the perfect bar for you.
I guess I don't have
anything left to lose.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Otae.
Hey, this place looks
really expensive,
but you know I really
don't have much money.
Is that so?
That's totally fine.
Excuse me!
One French Champagne!
What?
Didn't she get a word I said?!
Does she not speak
my language or what?
Can I have an interpreter,
please?!
Come on, sir.
Your watch, your ring, and your
sunglasses look pretty expensive.
So, why don't you
go sell them?
No, not my sunglasses!
Is this a highway robbery pub?
You're being so stubborn
about this, you know.
You're a diehard older
rigid kind of man.
In short, you are known
as a dork, sir.
Hold on right there!
Are you trying to say,
if I weren't so stubborn,
I would become a desirable old
and respectful kind hearted man?
So I'd still be a dork?!
So anyway, what would you
like to order, sir?
One French champagne,
if you please.
Thank you very much.
Good night!
Man, it's almost dawn already.
Hey, you, hold up a second.
What's that?
What does a monk
want from me?
My name is Katsura,
and I'm not a monk.
I know this is pretty sudden,
but would you be interested
in taking up a sword with me
and venturing out for
the dawning of Japan?
What the hell are you talking about
this early in the morning?
Katsura, you bastard!
Be prepared to meet your demise!
It's the Shinsengumi!
Let's retreat for now.
‐Hold on! What the hell this is about, bro?
‐Katsura, come back!
My name is Katsura,
and I’m not your bro!
All right, Katsura!
I know already!
This is not my day!
It is time for you to pay
for your sins, bomber!
Oh, I'm screwed.
Come on!
Why don't you confess?
I already told you,
I have nothing to do with it.
You have nothing to do with it?
Okay, fine, just tell us
where Katsura is and you can go.
Human language,
do you guys speak it?
Listen, man.
You have no documentation
to prove who you are,
and all you say is:
"I'm not involved."
That's the living definition
of suspicious.
I told you,
my name is Hasegawa,
and I used to work at the Department
of Immigration Control.
You'd know if you checked!
If you are going to lie, at least
make it a believable one.
I'm being serious!
You can even check it out!
Then, lets strip you down
and make sure you are
who you say you are!
Take off your sunglasses.
‐Come here!
‐Hold on just a minute!
Not my sunglasses, no way!
Preferably not my clothes either,
but seriously,
I really used to work
at the Department
of Immigration Control!
Well, you know you're a deceiving
overprotected red handed kook.
In short, you are a dork.
‐Investigation room.
‐No, not those!
‐Take your clothes off now!
‐As it turns out...
‐...I'm a dork no matter where I go.
‐Give up, old man!
Don't you ever
come back here!
I guess we got up early
this morning for nothing.
Tell me about it.
Now, the only thing I have left
in life are these sunglasses.
Damn it!
Would you listen to me
for just once in your life?
Oh, hey man.
What are you doing here then?
So your interviews
went south again, huh?
Yeah, I failed at every last one.
Not only that, but I had to deal
with so many weirdos.
Every last one of them
would called me a dork
and told me to take
off my sunglasses.
These sunglasses are a part
of my face.
They don't come off, man.
You Idiot!
Stop blaming everything
on your sunglasses!
Blaming a rock when you trip over
it doesn't change anything!
Just take them off!
Yes, all you need to do
is take off your sunglasses.
So, are you telling me
to become a sell out now?
Do you think I can change
myself at this stage of my life?
That's enough.
Sit down.
Hey, Master Chef.
Give him something that
reminds him of his mama's cooking.
‐Now how the hell would I know that?
‐Dumpling soup.
Did you not have
a mother growing up?
Just get us some
digestive biscuits!
What kind of mother
did you have?!
Listen, Hasegawa.
It's okay to have your own
values and rules that you live by,
but if they aren't helping
you be happy
or get where you want to be
maybe its time to re‐evaluate
your values and beliefs.
You gotta be open to
different ways to do things,
and explore all the possibilities,
and eventually, you'll be able
to figure out what it is
that is truly important to you
and your happiness.
You can worry about your sunglasses
after all that, you know.
I am...
Who am I?
My name is Taizo Hasegawa.
It's very nice to meet you.
I've finally lost
my sunglasses, too.
So, what kind of work did you do
before, Mr. Hasegawa?
I was fighting against evil aliens
in order to save the Earth.
You're very funny.
You're hired.
I didn't realize that just
taking off my sunglasses
could make this much
difference in my life.
I hate having young people
tell me what to do,
but people are more
than just their age in life.
There are people in this world
who've been alive for a lot less time
than I have yet experienced
a lot more in their time.
Hello, sir.
Where to?
Don't simply call him sir!
Call him Captain!
Cut it out, you guys!
I'm very sorry about that, driver.
Please take us
to the Cultural Center.
All right, Captain.
Hurry up! Otsu's live concert
is about to start very soon!
Oh, yes sir, Captain!
I'm not the Captain!!
I am a sergeant!
‐L‐O‐V‐E O‐TSU!
‐Through my work as a taxi driver...
‐I realize...
‐Alright!
...how great it is
to have a destination.
Thank you, the back
from The Dead Salon.
‐I had so many customers.
‐To the hospital, please.
‐And each and everyone of them had...
‐To Kabukicho, thank you.
...a clear vision.
To Kabukicho, sir.
My life has definitely changed.
Drive until I see the dawn
of a new Japan.
But your boy's lost sight
of his destination.
Do you see the skuzzy looking guy
who is smoking over there?
Run him over,
just enough to not kill him.
What's going to happen
to me now, I wonder?
Where should I go in life,
I wonder?
It seems like I am the only one
who has no destination in life.
I am... I am... I am...!
I don't care where we go,
just take me somewhere.
There's one, a lost soul,
just like me.
I'm really bored, man.
Just drive me around
for free, would you?
Stop screwing around!
I'm not doing this for fun.
Don't be like that, man.
I just want to see
the other side of the horizon.
Who do you think
you are, my girlfriend?
So then, how's your new job going?
It was fine until
you got in my taxi.
You looked like a walking corpse
when I saw you the other day,
but I think you look
slightly better today, man.
As if... really?
Nothing has changed.
I changed my job,
that's all.
But I still don't have
a purpose.
I don't have a clear vision
for my future.
I have no destination.
Everyone's in that same boat, man.
Just keep crawling
through the mud,
and you'll find
a destination eventually.
I really don't think
that's how it works.
Because in this show,
at least,
you and I are the only ones
with soulless eyes.
Hey, its a customer.
Time to get out
of my car, asshole!
What is he doing here?
Start the car right now!
I don't want any trouble today!
I want you to take me
to the Ueno Zoo.
And make it snappy.
Haven't I seen the two of you
somewhere before?
I don't think you would have.
Who are you?
That thing on your head,
isn't that a bit indecent?
Like some believe
the Earth itself is,
since we all have
the same flat faces.
I guess so.
Never mind then!
Well then, Mr. Hasegawa,
I have a knitting class to get to!
Have a nice day!
Hey, wait!
Please don't leave me!
Please don’t leave me
all alone like this!
I'd die from loneliness
if you leave me!
What are you, a hamster?!
Hey, just start the damn car!
Yes, I'm so sorry.
It seems like
he doesn't remember us,
so we should be fine if we get him
to his destination quickly,
and then get the hell out.
Then why do you need me?
Let me go.
Nope, me scared,
me lonely!
Why are you speaking
like a foreigner now?
That damned Jii gets
his driver's license suspended
after all his years of driving.
Why do I, a prince, have to ride
such a filthy old taxi like a human?
Hey, silver hair!
If you have nothing to do,
how about you take care
of your customer?
Well, I say to take care
of your customer,
but why are you washing
my hair of all things?
So, boss, are you here
on business?
I'm not your boss!
What the hell
is wrong with you?
It's just that, I wanted to see
a panda all of a sudden.
I've got shampoo
in my eyes!
‐You're doing that on purpose, aren't you?!
‐I see.
You've come to see
a panda, have you?
‐Ow, the shampoo!
‐But don't be fooled by them.
‐Stop it! There's shampoo in my eyes!
‐It's said that they eat only bamboo...
‐...and nothing else.
‐Shampoo!
But we don't know what they're really
eating behind closed doors.
They may even be gorging
on overpriced hotspots.
Idiot, are you trying
to get yourself killed?!
What were you thinking?
Hey, you're that guy
from the job interview.
Old man, this is an emergency!
Please give us a ride!
Oh, I can't breathe!
Sachiko, Sachiko my wife,
she's suddenly gone into labor!
Aaah! My best feature has been
pulled right off, damn it!
Oh, man!
The car stopped so suddenly
that it came right off.
What are you going to do
about this?
Without that, I'm no different
from a regular human!
I'm like an assistant manager!
Don't worry about it.
You look like a manager
at the very least.
That's not my point, you idiot!
Look, if it comes off this easily,
it means you didn't really need it.
Stop! Quit it, you two!
There's a woman here who's about
to give birth at any moment!
Hey Gin, is there a
maternity clinic around here?
Uh, nope.
You'd have to turn back.
Well, then we will just
have to go back.
Are you kidding me?!
I lost my best feature
and now you're telling me
that we're going back?
Give me a break!
I'm seeing the damn pandas
no matter what happens!
Hurry up and get
this car moving!
But Your Highness, can't you
direct a tiny fraction
of your love for pandas
towards human beings?
Understand, a human baby
can be really cute too, you know.
Look here!
I couldn't care less!
You lot of conceited, inferior monkeys
don't deserve any love!
I don't give a monkeys left nut what
happens to a human baby or two!
Who do you think I am?!
I'll have you know that I'm...
Who the hell are you?
You're just some assistant
manager, aren't you?
Cut it out, Gin.
What do you think you're going to do
to the Prince back there?
I understand your point,
Prince Hata.
You really want to see
a panda, right?
And I just remembered that there's
actually a panda really close by.
What? Really?
Where?
Just look at your face in
the mirror tomorrow morning!
Hey, you two hoodlums!
A seat just opened up.
You need a ride?
Old man, I seriously
owe you one!
Hasegawa, you know what?
I think that you look
a lot better...
with your sunglasses on,
I have to say.
I do, don't I?
‐Come on, let's go.
‐Hey, old man!
I haven't seen you
around here in a while.
So, why did you come back?
Well... that is because...
I was fired from my job again,
so I'm back.
Why were you fired
from your job again?
Oh well, that's...
because I decided
to be true to myself.
But the thing is,
I'm not upset about it at all.
I've decided to live my life
doing what I think is right
instead of trying
to make everyone happy.
Good for you, but that doesn't change
the fact that you're a corny,
single, middle‐aged man,
you jobless loser.
Let's go, Sadaharu.
See ya, delusional old
reality ignoring knucklehead.
Or dork for short.
That girl is one tough cookie.
Takasugi, what are you doing here?
I heard there was a festival.
So I just had to come here
and check it out.
Don't tell me.
You dumb bastard.
The next episode...
"Sons Only Take After Their Father's
Negative Attributes."