The land of the samurai.
There was a time,
a long time ago
when our country
was called by that name.
With the arrival of
the "Amanto" or Sky People
and the Sword Ban
enacted 20 years ago,
the samurai class
fell into decline.
In these hard times there was one man
left with the spirit of the samurai.
His name is Gintoki Sakata,
a reckless jack of all trades
with a serious sweet tooth
and a big heart.
Due to some rather
unexpected events,
I, Shinpachi Shimura
and Kagura work here now.
The three of us working together
fight the corruption on the planet!
Is this that kind of anime?
♪Your Father is Bleep Bleep♪
Hey, hey, haven't you had
enough already?
I've told you a hundred million times
that we had nothing to do with it!
There are some things
in the world that never change.
The culprit is always the one
to claim they're innocent
and being falsely accused.
How stubborn are you going to be?
I've explained everything from
the beginning to the very end.
Yeah, yeah, like I haven't heard
that one before,
because people are always like,
"My kid would never!"
or "I don't remember!"
You're just as hard to believe as the
people who say things like that.
Come on, and just confess already.
We're not running a charity here.
Or what do you guys think?
Do you think you'll get off the hook
if you keep holding out,
because that ain't gonna happen.
I've had enough of this,
you balding idiot!
We've already told you
that we're innocent,
so quit wasting your breath
and open the damn door
right now!
We have places to go
and things to do!
Violence has four eyes.
Hey, you're out of character, bro.
What?
I risk my life getting rid
of that bomb for them
and they rake us over the coals
for three entire days,
those rotten cops!
Hey, at least we got out.
And thanks to me, we're not
their prime suspects anymore.
That's true, but why
they released us after Shinpachi,
of all people, freaked out?
Because they know someone who's
normally docile is more of a pain in the butt
to deal with when they snap.
These cops piss me off.
So I think I'm going
to piss on them.
All right, I'm going
to go puke on them.
Stop that!
We're on a show!
Control yourselves!
There'll be no end to the number
of times I'm going to be arrested
if I hang around
with you guys.
That's it,
I'm going home.
Don't get lost on the way home,
you morons!
Hey, hey, we can't have a comedy
anime without a straight man.
I suppose I don't have a choice.
I'll be the straight man
in this episode.
You... watch where you're puking!
Gross!
What's that gross smell?
Hey, just a second!
Stop that man!
He's an escaping convict!
Huh?
Damn!
Stay back!
Take one step closer
and barf babe gets it!
Oh, you scum!
Just for one day.
Hey, you there
with the mop top.
Do you know
how to drive a car?
Yeah.
Hey, don't think you can get away
with defying the authorities!
He's got me
and I'm scared.
I'm so scared!
I guess I have no choice
but to do as he says.
Come on, get out of my way!
After him!
Do not let him get away!
Well, it sure felt good
to defy those officers,
but do you honestly think that you
can get away with this or what?
Just turn right
and keep driving.
These days, successfully escaping
from prison is tougher
than getting six matching
numbers in the lottery.
I have no desire
to escape for good.
This is just for one day.
I'll be happy enough
if I can be free for just one day.
Today is a special day.
Today.
Today is a special day, huh?
I mean, if you're captured immediately
after breaking out of prison,
it'll definitely be a special day
that you'll never be able to forget.
Step on it, will you?!
I can't afford
to get caught right now!
Move it!
As you wish, old man.
Let's go!
Look over here.
We've just opened a new maid themed
teahouse you should check out.
That's so cute.
Move, move!
Get out of my way!
Pull over, you scumbag!
You can't get away from us!
Can't get away from you,
you say?
When you say that, it only makes me
want to prove you idiots wrong!
The suspect is headed southbound
toward the Sky Terminal Tower.
Requesting an immediate barricade
at the intersection.
Ten four.
What?
The road, it's...
We're not done yet!
Here...
goes...
Go!
We did it!
And here we...
We actually did it!
What? A stroller?
‐Pa!
‐Listen, my son and I already walked...
...a path of demons.
We are in a hurry, so please
allow us our leave.
That damned wolf and cub.
Doesn't he know that cars
can't simply stop so quickly?
I see them!
There they are!
Oh, damn it!
Hey, old man.
This way.
Damn it.
Where did they go?
Find them!
They couldn't have gone that far.
Hey, Kagura!
Come on, wake up already!
It stinks!
So tell me,
why are you helping me?
I'm not sure.
It doesn't make any sense.
Now you're all wrapped up
in this mess and yet...
Well, that's true.
But part of it is for
selfish reasons of my own.
I hate the police, and maybe...
Huh?
I just want to see you
through your special day.
Well, we're almost there,
let's hurry!
Right!
Hey, everybody!
Thank you all for coming
to my live performance.
Toda‐tes The look like poo!
Dates look like poo!
Today, just forget about
all your worldly cares,
and simply try to have
some fun‐gus!
Some fungus!
Okay then, you guys.
So my first song tonight is
"Your Father is Bleep Bleep".
So please sing it
with me‐dium rare!
Medium rare!
♪Even though everybody seems to be...♪
What the hell is this?
It's the first live performance
by today's up and coming
pop idol, Otsu Terakado.
You idiot!
Is life just some kind
of game to you?
You broke out of prison
for a pop idol?
You'd ruin your entire life just for
a moment's pleasure at a concert?
That's the kind of the mentality that
got you thrown in jail in the first place.
It's precisely because I ruined
my entire life for a moment's pleasure
that I realize that there are
moments in life
that you just can't miss
no matter what.
So let's just have fun!
L‐O‐V‐E Otsu!
‐L‐O‐V‐E...
‐Come along.
We're going home, Kagura.
Aww, but I wanna see more.
I wanna stay‐ke sauce!
Stop letting it influence you!
Look, this is practically a cult.
It's so bad.
The air is just rank
with human stank. Hm?
‐Hey!
‐L‐O‐V‐E Otsu!
Louder, can't hear you!
Sir! L‐O‐V‐E Otsu!
You over there!
Where is your energy?
Shout like a man,
you maggot!
I'm so sorry, Captain!
Hey, since when did you become
the Captain of anything?
I've been a Captain of Otsu's fan club
from the day I was born, huh?
Gintoki, what the hell
are you doing here?
That's what I'd like to know.
I didn't think you were one to go
for this teeny bopper crap too.
How am I going to explain this
to your sister, after all?
What do you care what
I do in my spare time?
I'm not a little kid!
Excuse me, you there.
Please don't walk around the concert
hall during the performance.
You're spoiling it for the rest
of the audience of fans.
I'm very sorry, Miss Manager.
I'll throw this intruder out.
Oh, you're from the fan club?
I'll leave it to you then.
Today is the girl's
first live show
and we have to make sure
it's a success.
L‐O‐V‐E Otsu!
Oh no!
‐Yeah!
Yeah!
♪Even though, everybody seems
to be saying it,♪
♪when the time comes,
I can't help but choke.♪
♪Your father is Bleep Bleep!♪
Otsu Terakado's second single.
"Your Father is Bleep Bleep"
will be in stores soon!
If you don't buy it,
I'll rip off your mole.
I see.
So you're the one who is
managing Otsu, is that so?
So the two of you, mother and
daughter, made it this far together.
That's impressive.
Hearing that from you
doesn't make me happy.
Not in the slightest.
I'm surprised you have the nerve
to show your face after all this time,
and now that I think about it,
aren't you still
supposed to be in jail?
Why are you even here?
I'm honestly amazed and I can see you
haven't changed one bit in 13 years.
You're free to live your life
however you please, you know,
but do you ever stop to think
that there might be people who
have to suffer for your actions,
people like your daughter and I?
For no other reason
than being your daughter,
Otsu has had to endure so much.
Hey, Otsu, what would you say is the key
selling point of your second single,
"Your Father is Bleep Bleep"?
I'd say it has to be
like the hidden meaning
behind the words
bleep bleep, you know.
What would make me the most happy
is if people would appreciate
it's more mature implications!
Otsu, tomorrow is your first
solo concert, right?
How are you feeling?
I'm feeling excited
to do my very best!
Come to think of it, Otsu.
Your mother is your manager,
isn't she?
Yes.
What does your father have to say
about your concert tomorrow?
My father...
Her father is not here
because he died 13 years ago.
Oh, is that true, Miss Otsu?
She doesn't know what to say.
It's nobody else's fault
but yours, you know,
that Otsu has had
to suffer like that.
Just go away, please.
And please never show up
in our presence ever again.
And don't force her to relive
any more painful memories...
like the fact that her father
is a murderer.
Hey, man, you want some gum?
What do I look like,
a teenage kid to you?
You know, the secret
to enjoying life
is to hold on
to the kid inside of you.
Well, busting out of jail just to see
your daughter's big moment on stage
is something you can't do
unless you're a childish idiot.
That's not how it is at all,
you idiot!
I once made a promise
to her a long time ago.
♪I want to be a music idol.
La‐la‐la‐la...♪
You're tone deafness
must be hereditary!
You really are my daughter!
Just you wait.
I'm gonna practice
and get better,
and one day become
a real idol singer.
If you could become
a professional singer,
then there's hope
for even the crickets.
Oh shut up, you meanie!
If I say I'll be
an idol singer, I will!
How about that,
my little girl?
Well, listen, if you ever
do go pro,
then I'll bring a million roses
and be the first to be
at your concert, alright, baby?
You absolutely mean that?
Yeah, I promise you I will.
She's probably forgotten it by now.
That was 13 years ago.
Even if she did remember,
she'd probably want to forget it.
Not when she knows her stupid father
is a convicted murderer.
I can't even begin to imagine how much
she's had to suffer because of me.
She probably doesn't even
want to see my face.
I'm going back.
I forgot to buy the roses, anyway.
‐Sorry for all the trouble.
‐Gintoki!
What's up?
The venue has gone
off the walls
because some skitzo suddenly
went kablooey and...!
Speak normally.
I can't understand
a word you're saying.
What I was saying is...
there was this Amanto
in the concert hall.
And the problem is, he is apparently
one of those nut jobs
from the Love‐Cannibal Clan
that eats the objects of their desire!
L‐O‐V‐E Otsu!
I can't control myself anymore!
And that's why I came here
to report it to you, Gintoki.
So apparently, you can speak
normally, huh?
Hey, Captain!
Member number 49
has gone totally berserk!
Wait, he was one of us?
I thought he was some kind
of inflatable mascot!
Stop it, you big balloon!
Otsu!
I'm so hungry!
Otsu, my dearest,
become one with me...
inside my stomach!
Oh no, Otsu is in danger!
Oh! We have to get out
of here now, Otsu!
I can't.
My legs won't move.
What do I do?
Who... who on earth is that?!
Otsu, quickly make a run for it!
Hurry up and get him!
It's our duty to defend
Otsu as well, come on!
Hey!
Hang in there
and open your eyes!
Oh, look, he's awake.
You are crazy,
you know that?
Pulling a mad stunt like that.
But um... tell me,
who are you?
Just a very big fan of yours.
Kagura!
That's right, it's me!
I came to help
"you've got mail"!
What are you doing?
Just like in mine‐ority report!
Gintoki!
You better stop getting
in Duh‐way‐ne Johnson, then!
Well I think it's about time
you got lost‐ar is born!
Hold it right there!
I'm the one that's going to
protect Otsu girls one cup!
He went there?
Hey, old man.
Sorry, but that was
all I could find.
It's not quite a million roses,
but you can make up
for the rest with your affection.
You idiot.
There's no way that she'd remember
that promise I'd made.
But at this point,
I guess it doesn't matter whether
she remembers the promise or not.
I'll keep my promise
for my own sake.
Otsu...
you'd better take it to the top.
Hey there!
Next time, you'd better
bring roses, okay?
Until then, I'll always be waiting
for you on the stage, Dad.
I promise you!
Yo... you done with your emotional
farewells, pops?
You idiot.
This ain't a permanent farewell.
I swear.
I'll come back
to see her again.
Hey, everyone!
A lot has happened, but let's start
over‐head chop!
Over head chop!
So now, please listen up!
I dedicate this next song
to my dearest father.
It's called
"Your Father is Bleep Bleep."
Please listen‐dian death‐lock!
Yeah!
♪Your father is Bleep Bleep!♪
♪Even though, everybody seems
to be saying it♪
♪when the time comes,
I can't help but choke♪
♪Even though, everybody seems
to be saying it,♪
♪when the time comes,
I can't help but choke♪
♪Your father is Bleep‐Bleep♪
Next time, I'll come
with my head held high.
♪Your father is Bleep Bleep♪
♪That is a tempting invitation♪
♪That is...♪
♪a secret intonation♪
♪Your father is Bleep Bleep♪
In Kabukicho, Japanese hosts
are on the decline due to the
rapidly intensifying emergence
of good‐looking foreign hosts.
Yet, here we see two men,
sporting their god‐given gifts
of blonde hair and butt‐chin.
The mysterious vagabond,
Kintoki Sakata,
and the former No. 1 host the
butt‐chinned Shinpachi...
Having gained a female Chinese Mafia
boss as a their patron,
the two men knife their way through
the corrupt streets of the night!
A new show, "Kin Tama"
starts next week!
Gin! We're definitely not doing
a show like that!
‐In Kabukicho, Japanese hosts are...
‐Gin!
Please be serious and tell us
about the next episode!
Come on, really? Man, what a pain
in the butt. Fine then.
The next episode....
And clean up after your pets,
for pet's sake!