Make yourself useful...
and do some volunteer work
or something!
Oh! The Captain's crying!
Incredible!
Otsu's new song must be her
very greatest hit ever!
Yeah...
it moves me even more than
her other songs.
It might even be her best since
"Your Father is Bleep Bleep"?
Listen!
I hear she's appearing on that show,
"Edo's Got Talent"
A Lately, Otsu's becoming
more and more famous.
I'm very happy that Otsu
is becoming a big star...
but at the same time, it
also makes me a bit sad..
What's wrong?
Sergeant?
C‐Captain...
check this out.
What's thebig deal?
Who cares about some stupid
kid's puppy love?
More importantly, what happened
to my drama rerun?
Whatever happened with the battle
between Lotty and Bunny?
Just when Lotty and Bunny were
about to finally have their
showdown, the fearsome Alien Emperor
attacked the Earth.
Lotty and Bunny joined forces
to defeat the Emperor, the end.
Are you serious?
How do you know all that?
Yesterday was the final episode,
right, Sadaharu?
Oh my god, and I totally missed it!
You mean I'll never get
to see Lotty again?
Never mind that, Shinpachi's
been acting strange.
He keeps tearing days off
the calendar one by one.
Hey...
you aren't gonna bend
space time by doing that.
Stop running away from reality...
This is what happens when
you fall in love with an idol.
I mean, I'm a fan of the weather lady,
but I know better than to...
...Maya Sizitzy, juar got
married last month.
That's great, you might
actually manage
to do it with that black
hole in your heart.
Wow!
Shinpachi's body automatically
reacts to errands even
when he's lost his sanity!
Uh, we don't need
any newspapers...
Otsu?
"Break up with the guy,
or I'll kill you berry much."
Is the writer of this witless note
one of your witless
fans or something?
Countless letters like this one
are being sent to my agency.
It really freaked me out,
so I told my dad,
and he told me that
you'd help me.
Yeah, that father of yours.
Tell me, is he doing well?
Yes.
When I told him about all
these death threats,
he lost it and threatened
to break out of prison.
Then we'd better do something before
your father does something stupid.
Do you mean you're
willing to help me, then?
Yeah, but, the problem is...
the list of suspects includes
all of your fans,
which is how many?
But I have a feeling it's probably
someone in show biz.
Ever since these threatening letters
started coming in...
strange things have been happening
all around me, but the thing is...
It only happens...
when I'm in a TV studio or
out shooting a drama...
It wouldn't be possible for an ordinary
fan to do all this.
Hm.
‐Just break up with him, then.
‐Huh?
Break up with this guy, and everything
will work out just fine.
But, but I don't want to break up.
I can't imagine doing that.
I mean, he's the only guy
in show business
who's ever been truly nice to me!
No!
Get real, guys are always
acting nice to hot girls!
If we can't narrow down the suspects,
then all we can do is protect you!
I, Shinpachi Shimura..
will stick close to you and
protect you with my life!
He's back from the dead.
Come on, you two!
Let's get going already.
If you don't question authority,
you'll lose your humanity!
Wait, what's with that costume?
I mean your ears..
they are freaking huge!
Detective Munch, Baltimore
homi, I mean SVU.
Talk about a stretch!
Kagura, what are you
supposed to be?
Talking is overrated.
Of course, that leaves
you to be Dale.
I won't say Bing Bang Bong!
Oh.
So that's her boyfriend?
That's Goemon,
the lead singer of the nationwide
popular idol band, "Handsome"?
Wow, you sure know a lot.
You're a big fan, huh?
No, I'm not interested in sleazy boys.
I prefer the quirky type, you know.
Otsu, dear.
I think it would be wise
for us to not see each other
for a while, you know.
What?
But why, Goemon?
I don't want to do that.
I don't want to be apart from you,
either, you know.
But, well, it really isn't wise to...
upset our fans too much, you know.
I know better than you...
I know how valuable, and frightening,
fans can be, you know...
so let's just give it a little bit of
time, you know.
Don't worry, once the interest
dies down in the tabloids,
we'll be able to see each other
every day, you know.
Oh, Goemon...
You're amazing, Otsu,
the best in Japan!
Now let's shoot for
he best in the world!
Right!
You odd jobs people
here again?
What is the trouble this time?
It seems that Otsu is
being threatened by a fan.
So we have been hired to guard
her and solve the case.
Otsu. Always doing
something unnecessary.
But...
What do you mean, ma'am?
Receiving a death threat
every now and then is expected
a when you're a celebrity star...
If we were to worry about
every single one of them,
we would never make it
in showbiz, you know.
Yes but, weren't you
the one who showed
the threatening letter to Otsu?
What I wanted was
for her to be a bit
more conscientious of who
she is and her career.
But I guess it was a waste of time.
Who knows what'll happen now...
after that scandal.
But anyway, do as you will...
but...
please do not interfere
with her work, alright?
What're we going to do, Agent J?
Let me think about it, Agent K.
We should start by first
checking out that restaurant
where we should be able to find
illegal aliens in disguise.
Okay.
I make this look good!
Who's Agent J?
And who's Agent K?
Be sure to get home safely,
you guys!
So far, my investigation...
has uncovered several possible suspects.
The first is TV personality, Hairy Ding.
He's a multi‐talented TV figure,
who hosts a talk show, and also acts.
He has a grudge against Otsu
for revealing his secret,
that he wears a wig.
This is Mu, a wealthy TV producer.
He's been asking Otsu
out several times.
According to my research,
he's into girlie photo mags.
And then...
there's Humpty Wienerstein,
the director.
He's infamous in show biz for always
hitting on the leading actresses...
Sean Ross, the top actor
of suspense dramas.
There's a rumor that there were
plans for casting with Otsu,
but it was canceled...
Abby Cedy, the actress.
She's always complaining that everyone
mistakes her for Otsu.
These five show biz people..
are the main suspects.
You softie!
You're such a softie, Shinpachi.
Certainly those people are suspects, as
well.
But then...
you're also forgetting the biggest suspect
of them all.
The biggest suspect?
That's right...
He's always in the shadows of every
incident.
You're forgetting the fellow who
always happens to appear at the scene...
of every single crime!
Who?
The mystery shadow.
That's right...
It's the mystery shadow
who appears in so many
detective and mystery manga...
He always appears when
they don't want to reveal
who the killer is, but they still want to show
what it was that they did.
That's the mystery shadow.
Who are you?!
I'm Richard Moore, known as
"Sleeping Richard."
I can see you talking, you know!
Now, where'd he come from?
I found him dead drunk
downstairs at Otose's,
but I've always wanted to
do "Case Closed".
We're gonna get sued someday.
And cut!
Great!
Hey, Otsu.
Good, good job!
Awesome work, everybody!
Thank you very much.
All right.
We need to start
setting up for scene 12!
All right.
Mu is supposed to be here at
this shoot location so...
keep a sharp lookout, will ya?
Yeah, but I haven't seen Mu
around here at all, though.
H‐Help!
‐Huh?
Huh?
The, the producer, Mu, he is...!
He... he is.
And why is there a hot spring
at the edge of a cliff.
Hello viewers!
I'm your host for the mystery show,
"Serial Killer."
It began with a threatening letter,
but now...
we have a victim, and the killer...
is no doubt gloating
about the perfect crime
that he committed right about now.
Who is the mystery shadow,
and how was the crime possible,
especially in a locked room
with nowhere to escape?
The secrets will be revealed
after these messages.
This isn't a mystery show!
And it isn't even a locked room!
So now why was Mu ...?
All right, we'll take it from here.
Move aside, we're taking this case.
Don't screw up any of our evidence.
Move aside, now.
You're the ones trying
to screw this up!
Sea.
Roach.
Hey guys, we've uncovered
his dying message!
Would you two please stop messing up the
investigation!
Hi Goemon, dear!
You mean right now?
I'm at a hot spring location.
Oh, for a drama shoot.
Oh.
Definitely!
I'll do my best.
How about you?
Oh, that's simply great!
‐So now you like singing?
‐What a dufus, man!
Oh, yes!
You know you were gonna get hurt
if you stuck your nose into this,
you saw it coming.
You should've just
stayed at home,
peeling the pages
of your calendar.
I already told you, I'm going
to protect Otsu no matter what.
Oh, trying to show off
is a waste of time.
Listen, a girl in love
is like a wild boar...
they only see what's straight
in front of them.
It's actually not like that at all.
I owe Otsu my life.
She saved me a long time ago.
It was before I met you, Gin.
I was working part time, and well.
I wasn't good at anything I did...
and was always getting
scolded by my manager.
Just when I was sick of everything...
and I felt like just running away.
I heard her.
I heard her singing.
To be honest.
I didn't know what the hell
she was singing about,
and there wasn't any audience...
but when I saw her singing.
Just singing with all her heart...
well...
my eyes started tearing up.
Thank you so much!
Otsu probably doesn't
even remember me,
but she really cheered me up.
It doesn't matter what it is.
If there's anything I can do to help...
I want to do it...
to repay her for that day...
There might not be
much that I can do...
but I still want to do
whatever I possible can...
I owe it to her, I suppose.
I get it then...
If that's how you feel, then I have
nothing more to say.
Hey, Gin, hey Gin, big news!
Lotty is here!
Lotty is here to record shoot
"The World Is Full of
Masked Demons, Damn It!".
Lotty?
I want...
your autograph!
Oh, the broadcast of
"Edo's Got Talent" is ending soon...
I'd better use the john now.
Dad!
There's two dads?
Which one is the real one?
How'd this happen?
Carrie!
This is all Carrie's fault!
What good is that going to do?
I think I figured it all out!
I never imagined it would turn into
a fiasco like this, you know...
I know.
That chick will never learn to shut her
trap in front of the press, you know!
"You know"?
Could that be...
You've gotta be kidding,
I haven't even done her...
not even once, you know.
And I've been cast in the sitcom
that's going to be broadcasted.
That's right.
So I figured I better take
care of this first, you know.
Girls with no experience
are no fun, you know...
She fell in love
with me right away
just because I was a little bit
nice to her, you know.
I mean, he's the only guy
in show business
who's ever been truly nice to me!
That girl?
I don't really care,
you know, she'll just disappear...
anyway, I've...
Ahhh!
Wh‐Wh‐Who are you?!
Who are you?
You dare...
to call yourself a human?
You're mother is a...
bleeping bleep!
Hey, come on.
Enough of this.
My schedule is very full.
We may not seem like it,
but we're all very busy.
That's right.
I don't know what you're
trying to do here,
but frankly, you're a nuisance.
By the way, Hairy Ding,
why are you on the set
of a drama?
What?
I'm the, you know...
storyteller.
I told you from the beginning
not to get in our way, didn't I?
Yes, well...
I wanted to stay out of
your way, but then...
I found out just who the killer is.
So let's make it quick and
get it over with, then.
The killer's identity...
It is you!
What?
What‐What are you talking about?
I'd have no reason to do
such a thing.
If anything...
I'm the one who always
solves the mystery here.
Yes, but that's what
all criminals say.
You're panicking and starting
to get cold sweats, Sean Ross.
If you're going to accuse me,
show me some proof first!
Some proof!
Some proof.
Some proof, you say.
You are the real killer!
Just look!
That mole is suspicious.
That's ridiculous, I have an alibi.
Oh, an alibi?
I see.
Then you are the killer.
No way I am!
Tell me, are you just talking out
of your butt now or not?
No, of course not,
I'm not talking out of...
It's time to come clean because
I can see right through you
and your lies!
Who‐ who are you?
Who am I?
I'm Nancy Drew, teen investigator!
Hey!
Nancy Drew is really a blondie!
I already know who the killer is.
But that is....
Goemon.
What's going on?
He is the second victim.
No.
This isn't a victim, I heard him
talking in the john.
This guy is a real scumbag...
who has been playing with
Otsu's heart all along.
A playboy who just wanted
to take advantage of her
worried that the scandal
may kill his career.
Do you mean that he is
the killer, then?
Well he's...
‐That was...
‐Otsu!
You are.
The mystery shadow!
It really does exist.
How about that?
It really exists.
Otsu, are you all right?
Help me, please!
Hey, look!
A UFO!
After him, Shinpachi!
Right!
Stop!
This is a very fine work.
The treasure...
The treasure!
The weather for tomorrow will...
Sorry!
Commercial! Cut!
Go to commercial!
Sorry!
Give it up already, Mystery Shadow!
You missed me, you.
Aaaah!
Hey, you, man!
Show your true self,
take off your mask!
No! You don't understand,
I've been like this from birth.
I'm an Amanto.
What do you mean?
Uh, what do you mean
what do you mean?
There's no face to reveal.
I'm...
I'm an Amanto, and this is just how I
look, to be honest with you guys so...
I know you!
I've seen him before.
Everywhere I went, there was always
somebody who looked just like him.
No, I didn't mean any harm, I swear...
I'm just a fan of Otsu
and I've been following her for several
weeks trying to get her autograph.
In other words, you're a stalker, huh?
You're complicating things, you idiot!
‐H‐Help me!
‐You have be the killer!
You went through
her dressing room
and then you sent that death
threat letter to her!
No! What are you talking about?!
I did go through her dressing room
but I never sent any
threatening letter.
But then who sent the
death threat letter?
To answer that we need to
ask who would benefit
from Otsu and that guy
breaking up?
And that would be...
only Otsu herself.
The letter was sent
by the person
who wishes the most
for Otsu's happiness.
And that...
is her mother.
Yes...that is right.
It was you, Mom?
I told you...
I just wanted to give her a warning.
Just as you people said...
that Goemon is the lowest
form of a scumbag...
Like me, that girl has
no luck with men,
and she's stubborn to boot.
There isn't a parent around who
doesn't think of their child.
But, there are also few children who
understand their parents' feelings.
That's just the way things are.
Next time why don't you just try talking
to your daughter normally?
Yes, well, neither of us are very good
at being honest with ourselves.
Who are you supposed to be?!
Alright...
I see.
Look, Otsu, I...
Uh...
Oh, forget it.
I'll be fine, just fine.
I'm used to this kind of thing,
you see...
I have really bad luck with men.
The person I fell in love with
before was a leather man.
A leather man?
I know now that my mom was
only worried about me...
but I was a fool.
And he dumped me..
and now I've lost...
my popularity as a pop star...
and I've lost...
well, I've lost everything
in my life.
Look, Otsu, I, uh.
‐Captain!!
We came to help you out.
It's not fair that you're
hogging all the glory!
We're prepared to
stand guard all night.
All of you!
I'm afraid that we're all very
persistent, tenacious fans.
We're not going to stop
being your fans...
over a little scandal or two!
Thank you, Shinji.
No.
My name is Shinpachi.
Oh well, I guess I must have
passed out in the hot spa.
Case closed, join us in the
next episode!
Gin has amnesia?
You mean he's forgotten me?
Don't give me that!
You mean, I remember him,
but he forgot me?!
That sucks!
Who does he think he is?
The next episode...
Hey Gintoki, there haven't been
too many freebies lately, huh?
Yeah.