Remember to keep
the lights on,
and don't sit too close
to the screen.
Hey, just a minute there.
You on the bicycle,
stop for a second.
Your lantern should be
lit at night.
It's against the law
to ride without it...
Let's see...
Now tell me, sir,
is this bicycle registered?
Uh, I'm not sure, officer.
I borrowed this from a friend.
I see.
Doing a little shopping, then?
You get yourself some porno
magazines or something?
Uh, can I go now, officers?
I have stuff to do.
We've had lot of panty thieves
around here recently.
Have you heard of the
Masked Loincloth?
He broke out of prison again.
Well, I prefer boxers.
Good bye.
Hey, Hang on a second, buddy,
I need to see your
identification!
Hey!
Hey, buddy!
Hey, Captain Okita.
That long hair must be...!
Found you at last!..
Katsura!
Farewell to you, Katsura.
Damn!
Farewell to you.
Get him!
It's Katsura of the
exclusionist rebels.
He's somewhere nearby!
Keep looking!
We have to find him
no matter what!
I'm not letting you get away, Katsura.
That is...
Katsura, come out already!
We're not letting you get away.
Give it up!
We know that he's injured.
He couldn't have gone too far!
Damn it.
It doesn't look like he's here.
‐Keep moving!
‐Sir!
He's got to be around here!
Find him!
This isn't looking good...
They have me surrounded...
Looks like the end of
the line for me...
Good evening, madam.
I am Santa Claus.
Good grief...
Talk about misleading, huh?
It's your own fault
for sneaking around
when there's a panty thief
on the loose...
Have a bowl of ramen
and we'll call it even.
I run a ramen shop, so...
it's the best I can do for you
to make up for everything.
Ah.
My name is Ikumatsu.
I'm the owner here.
I am Katsura.
My favorite food
is soba noodles...
Why are you telling me that!
Would you prefer soba
noodles instead?
Is my ramen not good enough?
Anyway, why don't you tell me,
what were you
doing up on the roof?
Hm, oh you know how it goes...
I took a wrong turn somewhere.
Ohhh, so you got lost and somehow
ended up on the roof?
Were you trying to find
your way to heaven?
No, no, no, that's not it at all.
I made a wrong turn in life.
So then you are a panty thief,
aren't you?!
Everyone has a skeleton
or two in their closet.
But let me say this to you.
There's nothing suspicious
about me at all.
Go look in the mirror.
You'll see a suspicious guy
with long hair.
Are you...
No way.
I'm just, you know,
just checking the weather.
Honest to God...
Shoot, what awful weather.
Ikumatsu, may I stay here for a little
while until it stops raining?
Rain?
Since when has it been raining?
Alright, I'm going be completely
honest with you...
I pursue the Way of Ramen,
traveling to study the Ramen
from every region...
Your ramen is exquisite.
Please teach me how to make it.
Didn't you just tell me that
you preferred soba noodles?
Ramen and soba noodles are
basically the same thing.
They're both long and skinny.
You don't have the right
to talk about ramen!
Besides, there's nothing
you can learn from here...
Unfortunately, I don't get
many customers,
and the few that I do
get here are...
Ikumatsu!
Lookin' good!
Don't be so cold, baby!
Your dear little brother just dropped
by to see what's up.
What a joke!
You're not my brother, you know!
Now that Daigo is dead,
you and I are not related
to each other whatsoever.
Don't be like that, come on!
I've been taking the time
to come all the way here
just to see how my big bro's
widow is doing...
This used to be my
brother's shop, you know.
When he died, I was supposed
to get the shop,
but you said you wanted
it so badly, so I let you keep it,
but I think I should get a little
paycheck for my generosity, huh?
You want money again?!
I don't have a dime to...!
Greetings to you, gentlemen.
May I please take your order?
Hey!
Who are you trying to be?
Is this a French Restaurant?
Hey, hey!
Where'd you get the money
for a waiter?
My name is Katsura,
and I'm not a waiter.
What would you like to eat?
Did I hear three plates of fried rice?
Who said anything about
plates of fried rice?
We didn't come here to eat, so why
don't you just leave us alone?
Beat it!
Then may I recommend
our Full Course Meal?
Was that course "B"?
I don't care if it's a full course
meal or a full horse meal,
just shut the hell up!
I've got something very important to
discuss with Ikumatsu!
All right then, Ikumatsu,
three fried rice plates, please.
‐What's with the fried rice?!
Today's appetizer is fried rice
and our Full Course Meal also comes
with a main dish and dessert.
‐Today's appetizer?
‐That's a huge plate of fried rice!
Just shut up!
Ignore him.
Ikumatsu, hurry up and
hand over the money, baby.
I really need it.
The last time I gave you
any money,
I told you that was the end of it.
Besides, I heard that
you guys claimed to be...
exclusionist rebels to gain
the trust of people
and then broke into a
grocery store's safe.
You wouldn't understand!
It's a small sacrifice to make
for the big task
of saving our country!
Now we have a huge responsibility
and need money for the cause!
You three are no rebels,
you're just a bunch of broke thugs
that just want to take my hard
earned money!
Even the Shinsengumi
roaming outside
wouldn't even bother with little
insignificant brats like you!
This is why I hate people like you!
If it wasn't for people like you.
If it wasn't for people like you,
Daigo might still be alive!
What did you say to me?
Your main dish is now served, sir.
Shut up!
Beat it!
Fried rice again?
‐The main dish is fried rice?
‐It's shrimp fried rice.
And for dessert, we have a
nice bowl of ice cold fried rice.
What? Don't you have anything
other than fried rice!
What is this obsession
you have with fried rice?
Are you some kind of
fried rice maniac?
What the?
My stomach!
I don't feel so good...
‐Mine, too.
‐I feel...
a murderous intent from
my stomach I gotta go.
The john....
Is occupied.
You bastard!!
My stomach...
I can't hold it...
You put something in the
fried rice, didn't you?
Dammit!
We'll remember this!
Oh no!
It's coming.
What kind of a freak is that?
You did a really
good job with them.
What are you talking about?
All I did was provide a service,
just as all waiters do.
So then, weren't you seeking
the Way of Ramen?
Well, I did...
Let's just say I'm a waiter
seeking the Way of Ramen,
and leave it at that.
You're an odd fellow.
Sticking your nose into
other people's troubles.
Well, never mind.
Whether it's until
the rain stops,
or until you master
the Way of Ramen,
or until your leg heals...
I will let you stay here,
and learn from me...
Ikumatsu.
But listen, up...
I'm making you work your ass off.
What are you waiting for?
Weren't you going to watch and
learn to master my recipe?
It's just, I think there are
many things in this world
that people are better
off not seeing...
Like behind the scenes of
a Host Club,
or a boyfriend's
smart phone messages.
What is it you're trying to say?
N‐No, never mind.
All right, listen.
Speed determines
the taste of ramen.
Here.
Say, you're pretty good at this.
Hey, could you...
take care of a delivery for me?
Oh, my stomach hurts!
And it's raining really hard.
It's not raining!
What are you?
A little kid who doesn't
want to go to the dentist?
Oh boy...
She trusts me far too much.
So you haven't found him yet?
Don't worry, Hijikata.
We have everything
under control.
The Katsura dragnet
is closing in on him.
It's only a matter of time before
he has to give himself away.
I hope you're right, Okita.
Katsura injured his leg
pretty badly.
He isn't getting away.
What?
What is it?
Nothing, I just thought it
was unusual...
This is the first time I've ever seen
you take your work so seriously.
Like I said, it's just unusual.
You're the one
that's unusual, Hijikata.
What?
No other creature
on the entire earth...
eats sweet dumplings
with mayo.
Really?
You wanna try some?
It's delicious.
Absolutely not,
no thank you.
Remember, we're up
against Katsura.
Don't let your guard down.
You don't need to
remind me of that.
Excuse me, sir...
What is that right there?
What... What the hell...!
Remember, don't let your
guard down, Vice‐chief.
That damn long‐haired freak,
making a fool of us, like that.
I'm not letting him
get away with this.
Yeah, but, bro, he really seemed
strong to me, really, really strong.
Yeah, I don't know if we would be able
to win even if we ganged up on him.
Relax, you two.
Who ever said we're gonna be
taking that kind of risk...
Because I have an idea.
Mommy, I want him!
Don't look into its eyes.
You'll be possessed!
Wow, this looks amazing!
How thoughtful of you.
It's nothing...
everyone can use a treat
from time to time,
so it's just a little something
for all your hard work...
Good work today.
‐Oh! Is this...?
‐Can you tell?
I splurged a bit and
got a good bottle...
It's delicious.
Yohéi brews great sake.
It tastes delicious.
Speaking of taste...
I've been thinking
about this for a while.
Your ramen, Ikumatsu...
There's something missing
isn't there?
What?
I already know it...
I know that there's
something missing.
Then you'll have to add
whatever is missing.
The problem is that
it's not that simple...
to make up for what's
missing, that is.
It's a heavy task.
If you already know what's missing,
then I have nothing more to say...
But be careful,
because you know...
Ignorance is bliss.
Wrong phrase
for the situation!
That's definitely not
the right saying...
and besides, didn't you just say that
you have nothing more to say.
It's like water off a duck's back.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you calling me a duck?
What's that mean?
‐And Rome wasn't built in a day.
‐Oh really, so was it built in a nigth?
Every time you say something,
you're getting further
from the point.
Listen, all that I'm trying
to say is just that...
Yes, I know...
I can't leave things the way
they are, right?
Ikumatsu...
My husband Daigo...
He was murdered by the
Exclusionist Rebels...
We made a vow...
that we would become the
top ramen shop in Edo City...
but he got involved in a
terrorist attack...
and that was it...
"Saving the country" by hurting
innocent people is total bullshit...
Spinning their noble‐sounding words,
and then destroying
whatever they want...
How many of them,
I wonder, truly care about
saving their country at all?
If they can't even save the people
right in front of them,
there's no way they can
save this country...
Patriots my ass...
Samurai my ass...
I hate them all.
Listen, I already told you I can't
hire someone like you.
Look...
there's nobody who would want
anything to do with you at all...
Ikumatsu, two pork
broth ramen, please.
Coming right up!
Tell us, tell us, Ikumatsu...
Tell what?
Who's the handsome
new waiter?
And are you two together?
You never let any men get near
you since your husband died.
But you did really well
with this one.
It's not like that at all!
He's just helping me out!
And what's so handsome
about him, anyway?
I mean, look at his long hair!
Men always look best in crew cuts.
That's what you say, but I bet you
have the hots for him anyway.
No way.
‐Really?
‐Really.
Ikumatsu, we need to talk
for a minute...
Ikumatsu is not here?
Where did she go?
Hey, listen, bro, you really sure you
want to sell off your sister‐in‐law?
Yo, my brother died a
very long time ago.
We ain't even related anymore.
She definitely trusts me
far too much.
I thought she would be a good cash
dispenser so I left her alone...
but looks like she's run dry.
It's better to trade her for cash,
and then I can sell that
ramen shop too.
I can't stay here anymore...
I can't risk hurting
Ikumatsu anymore...
And more importantly...
she makes my determination sway.
I hate them all!
Oh, look a new guy, eh?
Do you want some
bread crust?
We can party with
the money, huh?
What are you talking about?
We're going to use the money for
the rebellion, remember?
Yeah, right, bro.
You're just going to
lose it all gambling!
Why is her delivery bike
still here...?
Stop!
Just a minute, guys.
Hold on just a minute!
Yeah, just a minute.
We're looking for
an Exclusionist Rebel
who's been spotted around here.
We'd really appreciate your
cooperation in this matter.
What are you guys doing?
Are you on the job?
And that?
What's in there?
Porno mags?
Do you guys mind if we take
a look inside of it there?
Yikes! What are the
Shinsengumi doing here?
Wait!
Stop right there!
If they find out what we're doing,
they'll arrest us! Hurry!
There's no doubt about it!
Katsura must be hiding in there!
After them...
Katsura!
But how?!
Die now, Katsura!
Katsura?
Don't tell me...
that was The Katsura?!
The Kotaro Katsura?!
The real deal rebel fighter!
The Prince of Madness...
Kotaro Katsura?
We're in trouble!
Ditch the palanquin and run!
Greetings Sirs,
I am bringing you...
Your Full Course desserts!
I have just two things to tell you.
One; Don't ever pose as a
rebel fighter again.
Two; Never set a foot in
that ramen shop again...
Violate either of these rules,
and I promise that I,
Kotaro Katsura, will come to
collect your lives!
This is Unit One reporting.
We have found Katsura!
Send backup immediately.
Katsura!
It looks like we don't have
time to chat...
But Ikumatsu, thank you
so much for everything.
And listen to me...
I'm very sorry...
I knew the whole time...
I'm just like you, I guess...
I can't just ignore someone
who's in trouble
when they're right
in front of me...
I'm a fool...
and that's why you
shouldn't apologize.
I see.
Then let me just say this...
‐Thank you so much.
Katsura!
Huh?
Hm?
Good mor‐!
Oh, hello, Gin, long time no see.
Hey...
I got paid for the first time
in a while, so...
Let's see, what shall I have...?
Huh?
Wait!
I don't remember soba noodles
being on the menu?
Care to try some?
A humid city where it rains
constantly all year long...
That was our little nest...
It may have seemed like
a dirty sewer to others...
but it was a great place to
live for rats.
Papa!
The parasitic alien will take
over any organism,
from humans to dogs
and cats, as its host.
Ready!
If I don't stop it,
then who will?
G‐Gintoki...
I'm going with you!
Aliens just ain't shiiit!
Just tell them that it's from
Umibozu the Exterminator.