Lucky voodoo dolls
from Planet Wheeler, man!
They make any wishes
come true.
You make the wish and then,
you give it as a gift too!
Hey, man, is that for real?
Yeah, yeah, it is so for real.
You tell me, man.
What is the wish
you want to make?
‐I would wish for eggs.
‐For eggs?
I wish that she would get better
at cooking eggs.
Thanks for the purchase, man!
You know, this doll looks
awfully familiar to me.
What was it?
Huh? Why does a lucky charm doll
have a space monster tag?
Excuse me.
Run away!
Hey, sis, I'm home!
Oh, well.
Things like these
are all about believing.
Maybe a miracle
will occur today
and my sister's omelet will actually
be much better, even edible.
It's not like
I was cheated.
I got ripped off!
Hey, sis, I'm home.
Hey, sis?
But wait, she's not here?
Die, scum!
Wh... wh... wh... what the heck
are you doing, sis, huh?
Are you trying to kill
your own brother?
Oh, it's you, Shinpachi.
Oh, no! Stefan!
There's a hole
in Stefan's stomach!
You shouldn't come back
home at a time like this.
It's very confusing.
Don't... don't come back home?
But... but how can you say that
to your dearly beloved brother?
Listen up, I had a lot of trouble
while you were away.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
Your... your personality
has totally changed, sis.
What... what happened to you?
What happened to me,
he asks, huh?
Ah! Just thinking about
what happened pisses me off!
No! Stefan!
Wait, was that not a
key part of today's story?
A panty thief, huh?
‐Yeah, that's right.
‐A chocolate sundae?
‐That's mine.
‐...during the days I stayed over...
‐The hamburger steak...
‐...at your place.
‐...spaghetti Neapolitan...
‐Can't we do anything about it?
Can't we do anything
about what?
About the panty thief
I was talking about!
A panty thief, huh?
That's right, I said.
She got hit twice
during the days
I stayed over at your place.
Can't we do anything
about it?
about what?
I keep telling you!
The panty thief!
Yeah, what about it?
I swear this guy is totally
doing that on purpose!
You know, they say that
back in the old days,
women didn't wear panties
under their kimonos.
Young ladies, gals, girls,
princesses, all of them, no panties!
You're only referring
to a single age group.
Shouldn't you be saying
something more like,
grannies, women,
young women, and girls?
You fool!
When you talk about underpants,
panties, and no panties,
it can only refer
to young women!
Yeah, but only
old guys say panties.
What? For real?
Scanties are also no good.
Nobody says that
these days, Gin.
The one that I can't stand
are those thongs.
They took away
girls' modesty
as well as the pleasure
from men.
I'm wearing
a g‐string right now.
You're lying!
Theres no way!
No, I'm not lying.
I've been wearing
the same pair for years.
It's so worn out,
only the strings are left.
What kind of panties
are those?
In a way,
these are vintage panties.
It's worthless,
not even worth a cent.
Just dump it.
Anyway, women in the old days
didn't put on underwear,
they were perpetually
commando.
Wow, just thinking about it,
though you're a princess,
under that dress
you're a wildcat.
That's kind of hot,
kind of like...
She has this calm demeanor,
but whoa, look out secretly.
She's a beast,
like Rocky, right?
I mean...
Now is not the time for
your weird fantasies and lectures.
There is a thief who stole
my lucky panties, damn it!
Stole your lucky panties?
Are you planning
on going to Vegas, sister?
Hell, yeah.
Of course I am!
As a matter of fact,
I'm planning on it
being a high roller night,
you fool!
Don't underestimate me.
So, what exactly do you want?
Do you want it back
just for your gambling run?
Or would simply getting it
back satisfy you?
I want my panties
back regardless,
and then I want to slowly break
every bone in the thief's body.
Uh, really, sis?
Your statements aren't
those of a modern,
panty wearing person anymore.
It's more of a naked
jungle warrioress
from 20,000 years ago
type of statement.
A panty thief is the enemy
of all women, uh‐huh!
Big sis, I'm with you
on this one!
Oh, Kagura, my dear friend!
Well said, my sister!
Come with me! Let's pledge
our sisterhood with a drink.
‐Yes, ma'am!
‐Wait, wait!
Someone will die!
You two together
are way too dangerous!
This is so bad!
The deadliest combatants
in the world have joined forces.
Forget about it.
We already know
who the culprit is, don't we?
And who could it be?
Am I caught then?
No, damn it!
But maybe I am not caught?
Whoa, I really am caught?
What is this?!
Are you suspecting me of
being the thief, you bastards?
No, there's no way!
There's no way that a samurai
would ever do something so vile
and so low as stealing panties.
There's no way a samurai
would be stalking a girl either.
I may be a stalker, sure,
but I would never steal panties!
I am going to sue you
for slander!
You're the one
who will be getting sued!
So this is it for
the Shinsengumi, eh?
What a joyous occasion!
Wait, wait, wait!
Take a look
at this right here!
What is this about?
Masked loincloth bandit
strikes again?
This guy is the petty thief
that's been terrorizing the city recently.
As the name might suggest,
his costume is pretty peculiar.
He wraps a red loincloth
around his face
and he runs through
the darkness in his briefs...
stealing all the pretty
girls' panties.
And then he tosses them
to guys who can't get dates.
A very unusual fellow.
What the hell is this?
Some perverted version
of Robin Hood?
I see. So, that's the story
behind these panties.
I thought it was a present
from Santa himself.
You got a pair of panties?
And you thought
it was from Santa?
It's totally out of season!
Shut up! Kabukicho's Santa works
24/7 all year round!
That means the panty thief
thinks you're a loser
who can't get girls.
Oh, how pathetic!
Oh, but take a look
at your own costume!
Because it looks like Santa
paid you a visit too, pal!
This isn't... this isn't a charity
panty from the Masked Loincloth!
That makes it worse,
doesn't it?
Eh... uh... what?! Oh!
So, what you're trying
to say to us now
is that it's this guy who
stole Otae's panties?
That's right!
Precisely.
Almost every girl in the Edo City
has been his victim,
but due to his public popularity,
especially from
the unpopular men,
the police seem
to be having a hard time
capturing this panty thief.
So, the pervert thinks
he's a benevolent thief?
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it one bit!
How the hell does he know
I can't get girls?
‐No! The panties!
The 35th Wacky Mission
capture the Masked Loincloth!
‐Yeah! Yeah!
35th Wacky Mission?
And now a brief word
from Mr. Isao Kondo,
the committee chief executive.
Uh, the Shinsengumi exists
to keep peace in this city.
What exactly is peace?
It's the right to live
in this city safely
for people to live
in happiness.
The small happiness
of each person
will create peace
for the entire city!
And therefore, Shinpachi.
Protecting your sister's panties
is also the mission
of the Shinsengumi.
Boy, when it comes to making up
stupid excuses for missions,
our commander is really
the best at it.
Hey!
By the way, what exactly is
the Shinsengumi doing here?
We're here for revenge.
Right, Hijikata?
What an idiot
to give Hijikata
a pair of charity panties,
isn't that right?
There will be no mercy!
His eyes are totally serious!
Okay, our new mission is...
capture the Masked Loincloth
featuring pretty women.
‐Yeah! Yeah!
What do you mean
"featuring pretty women"?
Well, let's get started again.
This time, we've decided
to use a decoy operation
with the full cooperation
of Miss Otae Shimura.
Decoy operation? Oh!
I will offer my lucky panties.
It's gonna knock you out
like Mickey Rourke's cat punch.
Cat punch?
Just hold on!
That's too hardcore!
Normal boys can't handle it.
They'll run their ass off.
Then, how about this?
This packs the same punch
that knocked the famous
sumo wrestler down.
Knocked...?
No, no, no, no!
That's way too maniacal!
Hey guys, can you think
a little more about the brother
who has to see
his sister's panties
over and over again?
It's even worse than
watching a sex scene
on TV with your whole family.
And that's how a little boy
climbs up the ladder to adulthood.
You there, don't just dismiss
the situation!
I'm sorry to say, but seeing
your sister's panties is nothing!
For example, Hijikata once saw
his father wearing a bra.
Now, I get it.
It was so shocking that his pupils
are still wide open to this day.
Like hell they are!
I'm risking my life
as well as my panties here!
Stop messing around
and get to work right now,
you freaking idiots!
‐Y... yes, ma'am.
Big sis, you are so cool!
Listen up!
This thief is a genuine pervert
who prefers quality over quantity
when it comes
to girls' panties.
Therefore he'll definitely
sneak in here again.
That's when we can catch him.
I don't care if he is
the Masked Loincloth
or Masked Panty thief.
We cannot forgive
the way he tramples
over a girl's innocence
as well as a man's pride.
All pumped up and ready
to kick some ass,
we'll bring him down
with a single blow!
We'll stain his white briefs red
with his own blood!
‐Yeah!
Excuse me!
Aren't you all becoming a little
too psychotic over a panty thief?
What I mean is, do we really need
the Shinsengumi for this?
What are you saying?
Even I can...
attack!
Now, now...
I thought something
like this would happen,
so I brought these
from the warehouse.
Wait, what is all of this?
How should I put it?
Something like... land mines?
Not "something like"!
That's exactly what it is!
I had a hard time sneaking
them out of the castle,
with all the security there.
Takes a thief
to catch a thief.
Something like that?
Place these mines
in the surrounding area,
and I guarantee this old dojo
will become an invincible
and totally secure fortress.
I'm fine with it staying
as an old dojo!
Besides, isn't this illegal?
It's totally against
the Geneva Convention!
Well, they have their rules,
and we have ours.
Don't you talk to me
like some mom would!
A land mine is nothing more
than a weapon of war!
No, it's not.
The official name is
something like a land mine.
What?
Hey, Shin...
this here is a battlefield.
If this is too much
for you to handle,
then I think you should
just go home.
But, sis, this is my home.
So, how can I just go home?
It takes a real samurai
to call the battlefield home.
Well, that's not exactly
what I meant!
Accusing someone as suspicious
and cutting them into bits
without a second thought.
I've missed this.
Accusing? Whoa!
No, if anything we should
skewer them with a spear.
Even better would be
to crush them into paste.
How about we tear them up
and pluck them out?
Twisting, breaking,
rolling, and boiling?
Hey, you two are scaring me!
My back really hurts.
We're not working
on a farm here!
This is the most dangerous
landscaping work in the world!
Quit being annoying, Yamazaki!
How come I always get...?
It's because your blood
is so sweet.
The sugar?
We really don't care about
your blood sugar levels, Gin.
More importantly, I don't see
any signs of the thief appearing.
Maybe the panty thief
is not coming today.
I mean, not only today,
but never again!
Don't worry,
I know that he'll come.
What do you mean? On what basis
are you saying that?
Look at those panties just
hanging out in the open like that.
What panty thief could
resist such a target?
But the thing is,
it's too obvious!
You can totally tell
it's a trap!
Shin...
The thing about thieves is
that the more difficult the task is
the more encouraged
they get to actually do it.
Now, how the heck
would you know that?
And what if he is
a totally wussy thief?
Does it really even matter
who we catch?
Let's just grab someone
and say that he's the thief.
Well, if we can agree
on a story, it'll work.
Someone, as in who?
Agreeing on what?
Hey, hey, stop yelling,
Shinpachi.
If the crook hears you,
it'll ruin the surprise.
What I want to ruin is you!
‐This heat is enough to deal with, damn it.
‐What did you say, you bastard?
How about I ventilate your face?!
‐If you think I'm gonna even let you...
‐Hey, don't push me.
‐...then you are utterly mistaken, you idiot!
‐It's too hot!
You think we should
help them out?
If you're gonna fight,
then go hard.
Make sure your opponent
wont ever be able to walk again.
My fist wants to join
in the fight too!
Somebody, let my fists
taste your blood!
Hey, stop it, stop it now!
No more fighting!
You guys are just getting irritated
because of the heat.
All right, why don't we
take a break?
Shut up mite beards!
Shut up, ass hair!
Shut up, Mr. Tangle.
‐Shut up, you stalker!
‐Shut up, Gorilla.
It's just the heat, right?
That's gotta be it,
that is all.
Okay, why don't I go
and get something cold?
It'll help calm everyone down,
don't you think?
I'll be right back!
Ice cream!
A parfait or something!
Bargain Dash Ice Cream!
Seafood vinaigrette!
Beef bowl and spaghetti with
500 ml bottle of mayonnaise on the side!
Oh, some tea!
Alright, enough already.
I'll go get them.
Just chill out.
Good grief, unbelievable!
Oh, no, Kondo just blew
himself up!
Well, it was very hot after all.
I guess that would
blow you away.
No, that's not it!
He just stepped on a land mine
that he planted himself.
They could be anywhere
around this place.
What an idiot!
Uh... uh, wait a second, guys.
Please, don't tell me
none of you remember
where you set up
the land mines?
Oh my goodness!
The mailman is going to get
blown to bits tomorrow morning!
Is that what we're worrying
about right now?
Th... that man...
Where there's light,
there is shadow.
Where there's men,
there is a baldie
pulled by the elastic
bands of panties.
Tonight, I run the path
of men's dreams!
I am the Masked Loincloth Bandit
and here I come!
Hysterical!
You guys are priceless!
It appears you've prepared
a warm welcoming for me,
but I fear it's all in vain!
No, this sucks!
He came at the worst
possible moment ever!
Did you really think that I'd fall
for such childish tricks?
You've underestimated
the Masked Loincloth,
the greatest bandit
of this land!
If you come up here,
I'd fight you!
Or you can sit there
biting your fingernails
and watch as your panties
are handed over to perverts,
dweebs, cherry boys,
and delusional horny S. O. B.'s!
Here I come!
It's what you'd call,
taking extra measures.
Go, Yamazaki!
Beat him up!
You got it, Vice‐chief!
Get ready to die...!
What the hell
did he show up for?
You useless Shinsengumi.
There was a land mine placed
under the floor boards too, huh?
It sure looks like it.
Hey, that is...
You fools!
You can't defeat me
with something like this.
Perverts, dweebs, cherry boys,
and delusional horny S. O. B.'s
across the country
await my return!
Their voices give me power!
Can you hear that?
Their voices?
Masked Loincloth,
please, give us hope!
Rough nylon panties,
smooth silk panties,
fluffy cotton panties,
anything is fine!
Just one pair of panties
is enough for us
to live another day.
Enough for us to stand tall
and keep on going!
Can you hear?
Can you hear all
of their silent cries?
Failure is never an option!
For the honor of the Masked Loincloth,
I will return to them all!
Wait there!
Keep your filthy paws off
of Otae's panties!
Come on, I haven't even gotten
to touch them yet, damn it!
‐Let me go!
‐It's your turn!
You gorilla with a butt hair
growing from your chin!
You're the missing link
in human evolution!
Do you think such descriptive abuse
would make me flinch?
Odd Jobs!
What are you waiting for?
Hurry, I'll let you
have this one!
Hurry up!
It's your turn!
No need to tell me that.
Hold on tight, Kondo!
Don't let go of his hairy legs!
No!
It looks like I get
the last laugh, after all!
Don't...
‐What is that?!
‐...underestimate us women!
There's no way
I'll ever give my panties
to someone who
won't even show his face.
If you really want this,
approach me directly,
naked from head to toe.
I mean with an open
naked heart.
I have no panties
in my hands!
Hey, sis!
Big sister, you're the best!
Hijikata, it was actually me
that gave you the charity panties.
What was that?
It was a joke, a joke!
You wanna die?
You wait here!
Stay right there!
The beach? Nah, no can do.
Apparently the beach is closed off
because of a man‐ eating alien.
But, There's a bounty on that alien?
All right! This summer we’re going
to be fly fishing for aliens!
The next episode...
I have a fabulous gift
for you unpopular folk
watching anime alone
at such an hour!
Send us a postcard addressed
below with your address,
name, age and the reason why
you think you can't get a girl.
We're looking forward
to hearing from you...
No, we are not!