In the previous episode.
Shinpachi saved a cat‐eared girl
from a drunk man on the train.
And so, this and that happened.
and he's been invited
to the girl's house
which is an incredibly
suspicious‐looking place.
And...
that pretty much sums it up!
What exactly is
"this and that happened"?
Could you explain in more detail?
Don't forget to mention why we're
following Shinpachi.
And so...
it just kinda happened, probably.
I've never heard such
an irresponsible recap.
And so, I can't really
be bothered anymore.
Nobody cares how
you're feeling!
Big Sis.
It's impossible for a lazy bum like
him to remember the details.
I'll do it...
And so, the cake was delicious.
‐And so...
‐you're just talking about yourself.
You two think you can get away
with it if you just tack "and so"
onto anything, don't you?
And so, the cake was
definitely delicious.
Fine.
I get it.
I'll do it...
The land of the samurai...
There was a time,
a long time ago...
when our country was called
by that name.
Hey, that's too far back!!
How many episodes
are we going to recap?
And so, I'm explaining
things in order.
And so, you just keep quiet then.
And so, I will not!
You keep quiet then.
And so, let's just get to
the opening song already.
So,
what is this?
Your wife has said that she didn't
want a molester for a husband.
She said that you're probably
too scared to commit harakiri,
so you should really just blow
your head off with this, yeah?
That woman doesn't
understand anything at all.
I'm such a complete
and total coward
that I jump at the
slightest noise.
I certainly don't have the guts
to molest anyone.
That's pathetic, Pops.
You should die with honor as
becomes a true Samurai...
rather than shamelessly
living in disgrace.
You're the type to jump
of a cliff yourself
whenever something bad
happens aren't you?
Life is not about living
with honor, no.
It's about enduring everything
from embarrassment
to eating dirt to whatever
else goes on.
Why did you shoot him?
I'm so sorry.
I couldn't bear to see Pops
like that anymore, Hijikata.
Hijikata...
why are...
people always so...
Why did you shoot him?
Why did you edit the scene
to make it look as if I did it?
And why are you sweating?
That's really pissing me off!
Everyone, come here!
Hijikata has gone mad.
Hijikata has gone crazy!
I don't know what to do anymore!
‐I just don't know!
‐No, no! Shut up!
‐Oh I think he's going to kill me!
‐It's not like that! It wasn't me!
‐Everyone, come!
‐Cut that out!
‐He's going to kill me!
‐Okay?
Oh, come os, now!
I can't find my police ID since
the day of that incident.
Ever since the
so‐called molestation,
my police ID and my wallet
completely disappeared.
And so, this and that happened,
and now we're following Shinpachi.
Good enough?
I mean the episodes
already started,
and so, the recap doesn't
really matter anymore.
Yeah.
And so.
Hey!
What do you mean it doesn't
matter anymore?
You're the one who
told me to re‐do it!
And I did my very best!
Hey, Erowitch?
I wonder where she went?
What's that?
What's this card?
So, what's this card?
Hey stop that!
It's not funny, you two!
The girl set me up on the train and
made me look like a molester!
I was drinking at a bar alone,
when the girl approached me.
She was a good listener man,
and even listened to my problem
with my daughter.
Oh, well, that doesn't matter,
anyway, I talked with
her for a while...
We got along really well, and she
told me that she knew a good place,
so I followed her and
when we got on the train,
she started making a fuss.
Stop!
Help me, somebody!
Somebody, help me!
When I woke up, I find myself
labeled a molester,
my police ID and wallet
had disappeared,
and all I had left
was this card.
I've taken both your heart
and your wallet.
Phantom Thief "Cat Ears"
XOXO
I really fell for it.
And at my age, too.
But let me say this.
She didn't steal my heart.
Oh no! My heart had
already been stolen
by my wife thirty years ago.
Wait up!
You bastard!
I told you...
to wait!
Who are you, huh?
Are you one of that
boy's family members?
Oh, his older brother?
What are you doing here?
So tell me, why did you
follow us?
Because you were worried
about him?
You really didn't need to worry.
I haven't done anything
at all to him.
Your little brother's virginity
is completely safe.
Because...
the only thing that
I want is love.
I am the Phantom
Thief "Cat Ears".
I steal love because love is
the most beautiful thing.
But you cannot see love, can you?
And therefore...
I borrow their wallet from them...
as a proof that I have stolen
someone's love away.
You BORROWED
Shinpachi's wallet?
What nonsense are you
talking about?
You're just a petty thief
as far as I can tell.
Your little brother was amazing,
you know...
I'm surprised that such an innocent
boy exists these days.
He completely fell for it.
He even wore those cat ears
I gave to him as a joke.
It was hilarious...
It made my heart beat like I was
in love for the first time again.
This is why I can't
stop doing this.
Hey, hey!
Where'd your fake
cat girl act go?
I mean, I kind of liked it a little,
you know.
Men are really stupid,
aren't they?
They can only care about what
they see on the outside.
Oh!
I just said my true feelings
out loud.
Silly meow!
Enough with that stupid
silly meow!
Because you smell like
disgusting cat litter!
And you are cat litter!
Women who can say
"silly meow!"
with a straight face
are good for nothing.
Silly meow!
Wow...
she's right...
Shinpachi!
Everyone, stop this already!
They say...
that all is fair in love and war,
don't they?
Let's stop all this.
Listen, I don't despise you for
what you did to me Erowitch.
In fact, I'm kind of grateful
for what you did.
It was short, but...
It felt like.
I had an actual girlfriend,
at least for a little while.
So then...
let me just say one thing.
Just kidding, you asshole!
What a bad ass!
Tragic or not...
love apparently helps
you grow up.
I've become stronger
since then.
I've learned a lot about
my heart.
It is no longer swayed
by little things.
I can stay strongwilled
in the face of beauty.
People's attractiveness,
doesn't come from
superficial things.
Things like being cute,
or having cat ears.
Rather, it comes...
from deep within their hearts.
Hey!
You guys, shut up!
Be quiet!
You're bothering the
other passengers!
But Captain, look!
Take a look at this!
It's Otsu's new single!
She's gone for the cat‐eared
look on the album jacket!
What a CAT‐astrophe!
Hey, Pops, is it true that
he's on the move?
You picked us up when
we had nowhere to go...
so we're prepared to
do anything for you!
The next episode...
Right after the opening song!
I called you all here
for one reason.
The guy finally decided
to make a move.
Hey, Pops, are you really
sure about that?
There's no mistake, our spies
always have an eye on that guy.
He seems to have been aware
of that and laid low for a while,
but his patience has reached its
limit and he's made a move.
I don't plan to be playing
reactive anymore.
If our superiors have
complaints about it,
I'm prepared to
commit harakiri.
This is a battle to the death.
I'm going to crush the guy
and all of his evil plans.
All right.
If you're that committed
to this to this action...
then so are we, Pops.
I'm counting on you.
Hijikata...
Okita...
There's just one thing I want
to check with you two.
What is it?
Exactly who is this "guy"?
You mean you don't know?!
Oh, Kuriko.
Sorry, sorry, I'm late, I know.
Did you wait long for me?
No.
I just got here, too,
same as you did.
I actually didn't have to wait
long at all, honey.
Oh, great.
That's good.
It's just that the train was delayed,
you know how that goes...
That bastard, who is he kidding?
Kuriko's been here for over
an hour waiting for you to arrive.
That's one hour of my
daughter's precious time.
You're going to pay for that
attitude with your remaining life.
Hey, Hijikata!
Get over here, I need a mount!
Just hold on!
This is the guy we're after?
Your daughter's boyfriend?
Shut up!
He's not her boyfriend!
I would never approve
such a shallow bastard!
Just shut up, Pops!
I don't acknowledge you as
a police chief either huh!
Hijikata, now that you mention it,
I'll never acknowledge you
as vice‐chief of the
Shinsengumi either!!
You shut up, Okita!
This is ridiculous!
I took off work to come here.
And you just want us to interrupt
your daughter's date?
I can't do this.
I'm going to be leaving now!
Hey, wait there!
I never asked you to
break up her date.
No, what I want...
I want to assassinate that guy.
That's even worse!
Do you really think
a pimp like that
is going to be able to make
my daughter happy?
Of course, I want Kuriko to be able
to make her own decisions
and love who she loves.
So I thought about it,
and I came to the conclusion
that I have no choice,
but to kill him.
I think you're overthinking
this whole thing!!
Hey Kondo, talk some sense into this
doting daddy here, will you?
My name's no longer Kondo.
My name is now...
Gorillo O Seven.
What are you doing exactly?
What's the O seven for too?
It's my unlucky number.
This year, I've been dumped
by Otae seven times...
Hey, look Pops, I'll help, too.
I can't stand guys
who cover themselves
in jewelry to hide
their insecurities.
Thanks for that Kondo...
I've known Kuriko since
she was a little girl,
she's like a sister to me.
I can't give her away to that loser!
Let's do it, Pops!!
‐Okay!
‐H‐Hey stop!!
This is very bad, they might
actually kill him.
Okita, we've got to stop them...
The name is Okito...
My name is now Okito O Seven.
Hey!!
This looks like fun, so see ya!
And so I told him that I was...
What a clever bastard.
He picked his spot well!
I can't get a clear shot...
and I'm feeling kind of sick...
Hey, Kondo,
how far do we have to ride
until we catch up with him?
We're not getting any closer,
you know.
Oh, for god's sake, you're on
a merry‐go‐round!!
You're just going to keep going
around and around and
around, you morons!
I've never been to an amusement
park, so I had no idea.
Although I've been to plenty
of adult amusement parks...
Don't be reckless, Pops.
You just want to break
the two of them up, right?
There are tons of
other ways to do that.
What was that?
You wanna join us now?
You wanna join the
assassin alliance?
I just came to make sure you
lot don't do anything stupid!
Unlike you guys, I'm not about
to judge that guy
just by his looks and make
assumptions about his character.
He looks like a bad guy
no matter how you look at him.
He's full of holes.
Aren't people born with
enough holes already?
Why go through the trouble
of making more?
Body‐piercing isn't
a capital offense.
Girls of that age are all like that...
always attracted to the bad boys,
the dangerous type...
Then they get burned and
grow up just a little bit.
Since when did you become
an expert, Okita?
Hey, I know I look
super dangerous,
but I've never been popular
with the girls.
What are you going
to do about it?
Well I guess it means,
for better or for worse,
both love and romance
are nothing but illusions.
It seems like your daughter's
created a false image
of that guy in her head.
But if she sees his true colors,
I'm sure she'll wake up.
Luckily, this is the perfect
place for that.
My sweet Shichibee,
I want to ride that
one next, honey.
Hey, hey, are you serious?
I can't go on rides like that.
Why not, are you afraid, honey?
I'm not afraid, but they make
me feel sick, you know.
So you're actually afraid,
then, honey!
No, I'm not!
Just go and ride it by yourself.
No, I don't want
to go by myself.
I want to go on a ride
with you, honey!
Wow...
Well, I'll be watching you
from here.
Quit blubbering and
get on the damn ride,
you snot ringed bastard!
Make a fuss, and I'll give
you a new piercing.
My sweet Shichibee?
Well...
Umm...
So I guess I will ride with you,
after all.
Really, are you serious, honey?
Hey, are you really sure
this plan will work or what?
Absolutely!
Okita's a sadist, and he's
good at torturing
people by pressuring
them into a corner.
Now crap!
Crap your pants!
If she doesn't smell poop by the time
this ride is over, I'll kill you.
My sweet Shichibee?
Tell me, what is the matter, honey?
You don't look well.
Let's get off the ride, if you
don't like it, honey.
I'll kill you if you get off!
I'm riding, so shut up!
I told you I'm going to ride it!
Shichibee...
Whoa!
This is tougher than
I'd expected.
How's it going over there?
Aaaah!
What?!
What are you doing
back there?
I forgot to fasten my seat belt.
I forgot to fasten my seat belt!
Hey, what's wrong with him?
He's acting completely different.
He's getting all panicky.
I'm a sadist, I'm not used to being
on the receiving end.
I'm a glass cannon.
H‐H‐H‐Help me, Hijikata!
Damn you!
Help me!
You idiot!
Ah I was so scared, but it was fun!
Are you all right over there,
my sweet Shichibee?
Oh.
My sweet, Shichibee.
How come...
you're sitting high in your seat?
This is bad.
You'll probably be disgusted...
But, um I...
I kind of...
crapped my pants.
Sorry about all that.
I don't have anything against
you or anything.
Thank goodness!
Actually, I, did too, honey.
I feel less embarrassed knowing
I'm not the only one, honey.
Really?
That's amazing!
We've got matching craps!
It's a miracle!
Yeah, we really are connected
by something that
we can't see, honey.
What?
Like we're...
connected by our intestines
or something?
Oh, wow!
You're so silly, honey!
Hey, what the hell
is wrong with you?
They've gotten
even closer now!
What the hell is wrong
with your daughter?
What kind of girl
craps in her pants?
Did you not potty train her?
Oh no.
They're moving to
their next ride!
What?!
With crap in their pants?
Hey, Kondo.
Hurry up!
Kondo...
Why's he sitting so high
in his seat?
Don't tell...
anybody about this, honey.
I can't believe this.
How could she still want
to be with him after that?
My daughter is
totally unbelievable.
She really is unbelievable.
I'll kill you if you tell anyone
about this, Hijikata.
Hey Pops, don't you worry.
Come on, your daughter hasn't
really crapped her pants.
Look.
That guy changed his pants,
but your daughter is wearing
the same clothes.
Is she walking around with a
crap between her butt cheeks?
Of course not, Pops!
Don't you know your own
daughter better than that?
Don't you realise?
Your daughter lied about crapping
so that guy wouldn't feel bad.
What did you just say?
Hijikata, are you saying that...
Kuriko isn't disgusted at all
by him crapping his pants?
You guys were disgusted
when I crapped my pants,
but Kuriko accepts the guy
for who he really is,
including all the filth.
Is that what you're saying?
Hey, Kondo, I'm disgusted
with you, too.
Yeah.
It looks like she really loves
that guy, doesn't she?
Hey, Pops, look at that there!
This doesn't look good.
They're headed to
the Ferris wheel.
There's no mistake.
They're planning on kissing.
Really?
Riding on the Ferris wheel
means they're going to kiss.
That thing was created
for kissing.
K‐Kiss?
Really?
Oh my god!
I never knew that!
Kuriko is in danger!
‐Let's go!!
‐Okay!
Mr. Hijikata.
Mr. Hijikata...
Mr. Hijikata, you're so
handsome and cool.
You must be so popular.
Not really.
Oh, come on!
You're being modest...
Mr. Hijikata, Mr. Hijikata.
What are you eating?
It's a bowl of rice,
Hijikata Special.
You want some?
I thought there was no
such thing as true love.
My gosh, Kuriko,
you really are amazing.
Most people would be
totally disgusted
if their boyfriend crapped
his pants.
I thought it was all over for us.
Of course not,
my sweet Shichibee,
I would never hate you
for that, honey...
After all, you weren't disgusted
when I crapped in my pants,
were you, honey.
What?
That's because, well I...
Because you?
Because you what, honey...?
Well, uh...
That's, that's because I...
lo...
Lo?
Lo...
‐Lo...?
‐Lo...
Wh‐What the hell is that?
Assassin Samurai O seven...
‐And we are taking your life!
What in the world are they doing...
Somebody, help...
What's that?!
‐Noooo!
‐Nooo!
Hijikata?
Who is that person?
I'm the warrior of love,
Mayo O seven!
Those who dare stand in
the way of love...
begone!
Mayo O Seven?
He's so cool!
Don't ever let anyone
come between you two.
Farewell.
Hey, Wait up!
I'll dump this poopy pants.
So would you go out with me,
Mayo O Seven, please?
Whoa!
What is love?
Next episode...
Dream...
Catcher!