You're not a bad fighter.
You must be a
ex‐exclusionist rebel.
And you're a former gangster,
aren't you?
Did you dye your hair to look tough
because your hairline's receding?
You're one to talk with
that weird curly hair of yours?
That's pretty heartless!
I didn't choose to be born with my hair
doing somersaults, and stuff like that!
This is the end
of the line for you.
Prepare to die!
Shishimura, you should look
behind you.
Do you take me for a fool?
I'm not falling for... huh!
Hey! We're still under
the Sword Ban!
What are you doing?
Uh, well, nothing, this is... uh...
‐Huh?
‐Oh!
That was a nice catch.
Oh, so you're practicing
for a sideshow?
Yes, exactly, sideshow!
Right buddy?
Well then...
‐Oh?
‐Whats this?
What are you doing?
Sitting like a pair of girls
who've just been heart broken,
wanting to run dramatically
toward the sunset?
Hey, Gin!
I'm so sorry, Gin.
Kato has left us.
Kato who?
Oh, the client we had.
Hey, Gin!
Just help me aready!
Well, I expected as much.
We're all getting used
to working for nothing.
There's no point in
being down about it.
‐Huh?
Honestly, I didn't think it
would work out to begin with.
Come on.
Gin, wait!
What a day.
I didn't know that Gin could possibly
be this cold hearted and unfeeling.
He's always been this way.
He doesn't do anything
when you ask him for help.
Kagura, what are you doing here?
Why are you in my house?
And why are you eating up
all of my rice?
I'm here to pimp your rice.
What does that even mean?
Is this really something
to be upset about?
Oh, hi, sis.
Otae, Shinpachi's big sister.
She's working part‐time in order to
protect the dojo her father left behind.
Gin relies on you
more than you know,
and if you can't believe in him,
then who will?
Well, I think you give him
far too much credit, Otae.
Like I've been saying,
you can't trust a man like him,
one who has the eyes
of a dead fish.
You're the one that can't be trusted,
you filthy stalker!
I can't believe Kondo
is still stalking her.
Yeah, I'm way beyond
being tired of it at this point.
I wonder what Gin
is doing right about now.
The Hiccup Bar.
‐Do you want some?
‐Oh...
What... what is that?
Rice with sweet red beans,
tossed in chocolate syrup.
I'm... I'm good thanks.
This stuff is great.
It helps you forget your worries,
for just one moment.
But once tomorrow comes,
everything comes back to you
and when it does, everything will be
harder to cope with, isn't that right?
There are some things in the world
you just can't run away from.
Especially, the things you want
to forget the most.
Maybe I just wanted
an excuse to forget.
An excuse?
I told you about
how I lost my job,
my house, my family, and
everything that mattered, didn't I?
Up until then, I used to be just a
regular salesman for a regular company.
I kept working day after day
to make my family happy,
and we were finally able
to afford our own house.
Things were really great.
If it was for the sake
of my family,
I thought I could do anything.
Everything happened so suddenly.
One day I was fired from my company,
and it was totally out of the blue.
I was upset, so I got drunk,
and then these guys took advantage
of that to stamp my seal on a contract.
They waved the contract I don't even
remember signing in my face,
telling us to leave our home.
Eventually, my wife decided she
had had enough of their harassment
and so she left and took
my daughter with her.
I said that something happened
to me every week, remember?
What do you think
happened last week?
I don't know.
‐Is that a letter?
‐Yes.
My daughter sent me a letter
right before my eviction from home.
"Daddy, I want to come
back home to you soon."
By then, I had already
given up on everything.
But after reading her letter, I really
wanted to give things another try.
Isn't it stupid?
Hoping that if I got
my house back,
everything would go back
to the way it was.
It's so silly.
But now I understand.
I'm a total failure.
Even though I worked so hard.
Let's go.
But... but...
Thank you very much!
Hey, aren't you
forgetting something?
Um...
Hey, so... I'm actually
unemployed right now.
So can we at least split the bill?
We are going now, Kato!
Going? Go where?
Huh? Come on.
Don't you want to get
the contract back?
Do... does that mean...?
I am Odd Jobs Gin.
I'll do anything for...
Brrp...
I don't feel so good.
Can we postpone the raid
until tomorrow?
‐Ehh?
‐I think I drank too much.
It feels like the whole world
is shaking beneath my feet.
No, this is an earthquake.
At least I think.
It is one.
‐Eh?
‐I can't hold it in.
Oh, no, I feel like
I might also... urgh...!
You don't have to be
that sympathetic. Oh God!
Man, what a headache!
This is a such a bad hangover.
I need some water.
Gin is the greatest.
I knew things would end up
this way from the beginning.
What are you talking about?
You were just complaining
about how cold hearted Gin was!
Oh! What about you, then?
Didn't you say he doesn't do
anything to help at all?
Can the two of you
just shut up?
Shut up, that's enough.
Are you trying to do my head in?
Oh, well, here it is.
So we're here to get Kato's
contract back, isn't that right?
But how are we going
to sneak in there?
Sneak?
We're not sneaking in there!
‐What?
‐We're going to break in there!
And you know what that means.
It means that we can just storm on in
through the front gate!
Wait! No, Gin!
Here's Gintoki!
‐There he goes!
‐Jack Torrence?
You're impersonating Jack Torrence
from "The Shining?"
Hello!
Is there anyone there?
You don't need to let them
know we're here.
This is very strange.
There doesn't seem to be
anyone here at all.
‐Oh.
Oh, the food is still warm.
Someone must have been here
until a moment ago.
You're very right.
‐It's piping hot.
‐Huh?
Is this really meat?
I mean, It's just so tender!
Hey, guys!
What do you think you're doing?
Come on, we're not supposed
to waste food, are we?
Yeah, you gotta enjoy the process!
You guys are a bunch of pigs!
What if the food's poisoned?
Did you think of that?
Relax.
Of course, it isn't poisoned.
‐Huh?
‐Oh!
So these are the mice, the ones that
have been snooping around this house?
Yes, Mr. Kariya.
Is that Kato I see?
What are you doing here?
Well, I...
Hey, listen guys, aren't you embarrassed
for laying such a predictable trap as this?
Says the person that got caught
by such a predictable trap as this?
I wouldn't have minded if the food
had a little more seasoning!
Enough, will you just listen to us?
No, you listen to us!
Give us Kato's contract back or else!
‐Huh?
The contract?
You mean to say you came
all this way just for that?
So... what if we did?
Shishimura, it looks like you
overestimated them now, doesn't it?
My apologies, Mr. Kariya.
Let's go.
We don't have much time.
But, what about the intruders?
Leave them here.
Oh, Kato, don't you worry.
Soon, your house will be
the very least of your worries!
Not that it matters cause you fools
are going to be buried alive.
‐Buried alive?
Launch sequence initiated.
Jackson Hole One,
preparing for take off.
This is extreme drone piloting!
Yeah, dude!
Oh! Oh!
Feast your eyes
upon this view of the Capital,
because this is the last
time you’ll ever see it.
It's no use!
Help me, you guys!
Why are you all still eating?
Hey, Kagura!
You need to go help him.
You're from the Yato clan!
I'm not falling for that!
I'm not moving an inch until
we finish all of the food.
These people...
Uh...
Hey, Elizabeth!
What are you doing here?
Ah, then Cobra
must be here too, right?
My name is Katsura, not Cobra.
Gintoki while you guys
were living it up in here,
we snuck in the back
and found something.
We came across this
when we were searching the safe.
What's that?
You found it?
You found Kato's contract?
I don't know what you're talking about,
but here, take a look at this.
Well, I would, but the thing is...
I'm not very good
at reading the small print.
So what do you think
this all means, Gintoki?
I honestly have no idea.
Then let me enlighten you.
The plan is to raze
the Capital to the ground.
‐What?!
A rave in the Capital?
He said "raze," idiot!
Let me give you
a brief explanation.
They're looking for a fault line
in the earth's crust,
which they will stimulate
using the Amanto made device
to trigger a giant artificial earthquake.
And with it they will level
the entire capital!
Oh, oh, no.
Its as if they're some kind
of villains from some anime.
But why would they want
to do something like that?
Those people who were
with Kariya are land sharks.
Their evil plan is to force people
to sell their land for mere pennies.
And their goal is the old city?
Buildings that weren't constructed
by Amanto are not very strong.
In the event of a large earthquake,
they likely won't stand a chance.
We have to do something to
stop them, or the Capital will...
But the main problem is, we have
no idea where the fault line is located.
Didn't you find any clues, though?
Well, unfortunately, we didn't.
So what are we going to do?
We don't have time to run around the
entire Capital looking for the land sharks
who want to destroy it
with an earthquake!
‐Oh!
‐Kagura!
You've had enough food!
Stop eating and break us out now!
You got it!
Hi‐yah!
I don't believe it!
Why didn't you do that earlier?!
‐Hey, Kato!
‐Yes... yes!
Where is your house?
Take us there!
Hey, Gintoki!
Where are you going?
It's very dangerous
to go on your own!
I know that, but we still have
to go there and stop them!
See you later, Cobra.
My name is Katsura, not Cobra!
Hey, Gin! Why are we going
to Kato's house?
Basically, their goal is to clear the land
in the capital and then take it all
for themselves to sell
for high prices, I am right?
I believe that's right!
Then why do you think
they tricked Kato
and took his house
first before the rest?
Well, I guess it was...
Ah! I get it!
It must be where
the fault line is!
That's exactly right!
So then Kato getting fired
and losing his house was all...
It was all a part
of their evil plan.
That's terrible.
‐Now, enough of this chit chat!
‐Hurry!
Uh, hey, excuse us!
What's up?
If you have something to say,
Kato, you better say it now!
He's right!
There's absolutely no time to lose!
The thing is that...
We're going the wrong direction.
‐What's that?
This right here is the earthquake
machine that was developed
utilizing the technology
of Drifting Star!
This is the device of our dreams that will
realize Mr. Kariya's ambitions!
This will mark the very
beginning of our reign.
‐Start the machine!
‐Yes!
Excavation beam
has been activated!
The ETA is ten minutes
to reach the target!
Onward! No one can possibly
stop us now!
Intruders!
Get them! Get them!
‐What?
We're here for an inspection!
We're the Shinsengumi!
Lay down your arms!
Government mongrels!
Oh, so you intend to resist
the Shinsengumi?
Interesting!
Isao Kondo, ready!
Toshiro Hijikata, ready!
Sogo Okita, ready!
Attack!
Hold it right there!
Have you gone mad?
Don't you know we're here
to take you down, you villain!
Let me spell it out for you.
This land right here is
in Drifting Star territory.
If you take a single step into this house,
it'll be an intergalactic incident.
‐Extraterritoriality, huh?
‐No way!
Uh, what was extraterritoriality again?
If any of you want
to enter this house,
you need to do so through
the official procedures.
Okita, what are you doing?
Well, if I blow this house to bits,
then we don't have to go inside it.
Isn't that right, sir?
Who do you think you are,
Michael Bay?
Heh! Now that you understand,
why don't you go
ahead and leave?
Thank you for your attention!
Now make way
for the main event!
‐Is that...?
‐Odd Jobs Gin?
He's here.
‐Leave the rest to us!
‐Oh ah!
Odd Jobs Gin is here and he will
take care of all your problems!
He's a civilian so he can do
whatever he likes!
This is starting to feel good.
Mr. Kariya, we should go inside.
Hold on!
It's time that you and I
finally settled this.
Huh, stop playing the role
of my rival.
‐You're just Mr. Sideshow!
‐You!
‐ETA is five minutes to target!
‐Good.
We'll escape as soon as
it reaches the epicenter!
‐Right!
‐Machine, to the surface!
‐Earthquake?
‐No! Did they already...?
What?
What the heck
is this contraption?
Does this really belong
in this anime show!?
This is too much, even for
a special two part episode!
So this is the device that
Cobra was talking about.
You get an A for effort,
but our plan is already on the verge
of reaching ultimate success.
No! The Capital is going to be...
Shinpachi!
I'm not letting you
get away this time.
You...
ETA is three minutes to target!
‐My... my poor house.
‐What?
‐Kato!
Idiots! Why didn't you
take care of him?
Well, he didn't seem very relevant.
Go, Kato!
I know that you can do it!
But... but how?
Hm, I'll cut you down.
I... I don't think I can.
Don't run away, Kato!
You know what to do!
You have to change,
or nothing else will!
To change?
You'll never be able to run away!
Especially from those things
that you really want to forget!
Dearest daddy...
I will change.
I will change!
Yeaaaaaah!
If I clear my mind, I can channel
John Cena's spirit!
What's this?
You can't even see me!
There is no way!
Keep my elbows close
to my body and just strike!
I will strike hard!
Yaaaaaah!
No way, really?
‐He did it!
‐Mr. Kariya!
We have to get him
medical attention!
I'm so proud of my student!
He's learned so much from me!
Kagura, you taught him to jab,
not strike head on with a sword.
What are you doing, Kato?
Now go and stop
the earthquake machine!
All right, yeah!
Um... um...
Is this it?
Where is it?
Eeeek, fifty seconds left?
But the speed was doubled!
Hurry up!
I don't care how, just stop it!
Ahhh! This is it.
Um... is this... or this one?
This must be it!
Come on!
It just broke!
‐It just broke?! This is so cliche!!
‐Nooooo!
Stop right there!
I'm not finished with you...!
Shut up, you plebian!
I don't have time to waste on you!
Just one kick, man?
Oh!
Time to end to this!
It... it has stopped.
Hey, let's get out of here!
All... all right!
‐Yahoo!
‐They did it!
Hey you guys, you know if you take
a single step across that line,
you're no longer
on foreign soil, right?
You know... Gintoki never
ceases to impress.
My side hurts.
This was our home...
our home.
What do I do now?
Kato, you shouldn't worry
so much about your house.
But it...
You are a changed man
now, aren't you?
Oh, yes!
‐Oh!
It's Kuromi of Yamatoya!
Hey, you stupid cat,
wait for me!
Odd Jobs Gin.
Ahhh! I want to know why
can't my sword have a Bankai?
Gin, look!
Look at the TV!
Huh?
♪Samba, ohh, Samurai’s Samba!♪
♪Everyone dance with
your sword in the air♪
Hey, wait, can this be...?
There's no mistaking it!
That's Kato!
Ah! Didn't you know?
Kato's been gaining popularity in
the entertainment industry recently
as a dancing samurai singer.
‐Oh!
♪Ole, Ole♪
♪Samurai’s Samba!♪
I'm glad he's doing so well.
♪Ole, Ole…♪
"To everyone at Odd Jobs Gin.
My family is back together.
Thank you so much!
Kato"
One year ago,
I met this unique man.
He was too barbaric to
be called a samurai,
but too honest for anyone
to call a thug.
The next episode...
Oh!... I forgot to be in the
second part of the show.