With Gin losing his memory
in an accident,
and Sakamoto's spaceship
destroying the Odd Jobs building,
we were, literally speaking
all broken up.
Shinpachi, you better have
brought my wooden sword!
Here!
Hey, Foreman.
I'm sorry, but after today I quit!
‐G‐Gin's back!
And that's how Gin's memory
was restored.
The only problem left is
somehow restoring Gin's place.
Hey, Gintoki...
So we're trying to repair
the Odd Jobs HQ, right?
But all I hear are fingers
being smashed
and the house being destroyed.
Every act of creation is first an
act of destruction, Shinpachi.
Yeah, but when are we gonna
start creating, though?
I knew it, this is hopeless.
You should never let
amateurs do carpentry.
You idiot!
Do you know how many
"professionals" out there
just take your money
to build what
end up as defective houses
these days?
Still better than defective people
trying to build a house, idiot.
What else are we going to do?
It's not like we have the money
to hire a carpenter.
Or what do you want, Shinpachi?
Do you want to get us kicked
out by that old hag?
Besides, you're supposed to be
a "Jack of All Trades,"
you should be able to fix
something like this easily.
Hey Gin!
Desperate times,
desperate measures!
No, wait, no, no, no!
Stop!
Whoa!
Wow! Wow!
‐Yeow, stop it now!!
‐No!
I can't.
It's rebelling against me!
You idiot!
Stop that wild horse you're riding!
Kagura, we're all gonna die!
Seriously, we're gonna die!
‐The switch, turn it off!
‐I can't!
I've never dealt with a
rebellious kid before!
If you don't know how to use it,
then don't even try to use it, idiot!
Take this!
‐Whoa!
Whoa!
Damn it!
What do you mean, damn it?
Why are you trying to destroy me?
Don't worry, Shinpachi.
People destroy their old selves
so they can embark on a journey
to find their newselves.
You moron!
You were about to send me off
to another dimension!
Kagura, don't you move!
I got it, Gin!
Okay, now it's stopped.
I declare case closed.
What do you mean,
"case closed"?
This place looks worse than
it did before!
Ding dong!
Excuse me,
but I have a delivery for you.
Dear Kintoki.
I know we haven't kept
in touch for a while,
but how are you doing?
I'm fine as usual,
flying all over the universe
from here to there.
Space is truly a great place.
The other day I had an opportunity
to stop by Earth,
so I decided to visit you.
But sadly, it seems like
we missed each other.
I'm writing you now because...
there was something important
I wanted to tell you.
Kintoki. You once said...
Hey, Ibaragi.
I heard you went to a
hostess bar again.
Next time, take me with you.
Or something like that.
But his name isn't Ibaragi,
it's really Ibaraki!
I wondered whether
I should bring this up
after all these years.
But it's just plain rude to get
someone's name wrong.
That's all.
Take care of yourself, Kintoki.
From Tatsuma Sakamoto.
P.S.
Sorry for destroying your house.
P.P.S.
Isn't it funny how you feel like using
"P. S." every time you write a letter? LOL
My ass!
This is BS!!
The content of the body and
the ps are totally backwards!
He destroys my house and all
I get is a "P. S." apology?
And he got my name
wrong again, too!
Even if P. S. means that
I wish for world peace,
it's simply unforgivable, man!
Birds of a feather flock together.
We don't flock together at all!
I really hope he dies.
I hope he suffers a slow
and painful death.
Come on, just take it easy, Gin.
Never mind the letter
or what he said.
What Sakamoto really wanted
to send you is this, right?
But what is inside this box?
I bet he sent you a
spectacular apology gift.
Oh yeah, now that I think
about it, he's a rich kid...
‐Money?
What's this now?
All right, all right.
Why didn't he just mention this in the
first place, that little rascal...
‐I tell you...
‐We can finally fix up the house now...
That guy jokes around
much more than I do.
Hello.
Thank you for calling Express...
Oh, this must be a dream.
It's totally illogical.
This can't be happening.
There were two
little men in there.
Two little men squished
inside that big box.
No, no, those were dolls,
don't you think?
They're just dolls.
Let's take another look.
I'm telling you, it's a dream!
Come on, that's enough,
I gotta wake up.
Hello.
Thank you for calling Express...
Yup!
It's all...
definitely a dream.
We're being tormented by
hallucinations of tiny bald men.
All right, let's take a break.
Meet you later after we take a nap.
‐Okay.
Hold on a second!
You buttheads!
Shut up and listen while we're talking,
you morons!
Yeah, listen, we're supposed to say,
"Thank you for calling the Express
Doorstep Delivery Carpenters!"
You idiots!
Delivery Carpenters,
did you say?
I've never heard of such a thing.
I have no idea what that is,
so go home.
How dare you talk
to us like that!
We traveled all the way
from a distant planet
just to fix your house!
Hold on just a second...
did Sakamoto send
you guys here?
That's right!
If we get a call,
we go build a house, even if
it's on a different galaxy!
Unkei!
And this is...
Kaikei!!
We're the Express Carpenters!
Next, please!
No.
This isn't an audition!
You buttheads, what can
you do looking like that?
I bet the two of you can only
make us a gingerbread house.
Oh, but then again, gingerbread
house, that's not so bad.
Don't be so shocked,
but listen up.
Do you know the mighty
Terminal building,
the symbol of Japan's might,
that made Edo an
international city?
That terminal, inside there,
you know that cupboard
for hanging spoons?
Well, it was us who made those!
It won't come crashing down when
the door is slammed closed, either!
That's so lame.
I once made a bookshelf out of
milk cartons, you know, man.
And it's environmentally friendly, too.
So what? You think something
environmentally friendly
like that is going to save the Earth?
It's not for the Earth, we just
don't have any money.
Yeah, we're on a
very tight budget!
What the hell are you guys
talking about?
You know what, it can't get any
worse than it is right now,
so let's have them do it.
Besides, it looks like Sakamoto
already paid them to fix our place.
Tell me, Do you know this quote?
It's something a carpenter
named Mokichi once said.
"Craftsmen who talk a lot
are never very good."
Remember, a truly good craftsman
never needs to talk about his work.
He lets his hands do the talking.
Which side do you guys belong to?
What is all that racket?
What's going on up there?
Is it them again?
That silver haired
punk is challenging us!
Well we'll show him who the best
carpenters in the universe are!
Who the hell are those guys?
‐Wow!
Amazing.
They actually fixed
everything overnight!
Take a look around,
the interior's perfect.
The skills of the best carpenters
in the universe!
Awesome!
They really are
amazing carpenters!
Hey, Gin, isn't this terrific?
We can go back
into business now!
Mm...
Something's not right.
I don't remember Odd Jobs...
being this bleak before.
Well, it's not our fault
you can't afford furniture!
We haven't touched
the original structure.
No, no, no, no.
It's not the structure at all.
No, something's
definitely is missing.
It's, um...
Oh, I know!
No wonder the room looks
so plain and ordinary.
The chandelier is missing!
‐Chandelier?
What "chandelier" do you mean?
A chandelier in a traditional
Japanese house would clash!
I don't know.
Are you sure we had
something like that?
I'm sure that we did.
You don't just look up
at the ceiling all the time.
You must've just
forgotten about it.
Now that you mention it...
I do remember
there was one.
Also, what happened to the stairs
connecting to the third floor?
The third floor?
We had a third floor?
I never knew that!
Yeah...
you guys may not know
about it.
But it used to be above the dresser.
The third floor was for
my comic collection.
Are you serious?
There's definitely something
wrong with my room.
It wasn't this small.
Don't mess with me.
The floor was enough
for 600 square feet!
‐600 square feet?
600 square feet closet?
That's bigger than
the living room!
Kagura, come on, don't you think
you're exaggerating a little bit?
Okay, I'll compromisefor
400 square feet.
I've never heard such an
unreasonable compromise!
Also, the toilet.
I'm pretty sure it has
a washout installed.
Also the bathroom wall
was all glass.
It had an arousing atmosphere.
Oh, I remember something, too.
And there was a karaoke machine
in the living room.
Hang on there!
We never even touched
the living room!
That should be
the way it was.
Have you ever heard
this story?
Long ago...
There were two carpenters who
competed to be the most popular.
One was a millionaire's son,
who was also good
at running business.
His name was Gohei.
The other was an odd
guy named Mokichi.
He didn't care much
about being paid at all.
Mokichi had no interest in worldly
success, but Gohei was different.
Every day, Gohei schemed
to get rid of Mokichi
so that he could be the most
popular carpenter in Edo City.
Before long, Mokichi's
reputation began to wane.
Gohei was behind this.
He pulled strings around
and made sure Mokichi
got the worst kind of cases.
Mokichi had all the impossible
and difficult jobs forced on him,
and eventually, Mokichi was
no longer able to find work.
Exactly as Gohei had planned.
Mokichi's popularity dwindled rapidly
and Gohei's day had come.
Or so it seemed...
But suddenly Mokichi's
troubles had dissolved.
Years later, Mokichi's popularity
surpassed that of Gohei's
and he was the top carpenter in Edo City.
You probably want to know why.
Gohei wanted to know, too.
You bastard, what kind of
dirty trick did you pull?
Weren't you the one getting forced
to do all the impossible jobs?
Mokichi replied.
Yes, you are right.
And it was very difficult work,
but it taught me more tha
I'veever known about carpentry.
I sure am grateful
that it happened.
Mokichi is the bomb!
Mokichi probably
didn't even realize
he was being tricked by Gohei.
He loved carpentry so much
that he welcomed the
challenges presented!
Isn't that what it really means
to be a craftsman?
Damn it!
That punk has
sparked my soul!
Yeah, Bro!
No matter how you look at it,
they're playing us!
Like marionettes on a string!
I know, I know,
but I just can't stop it.
My craftmen's blood is all
fired up and boiling.
Me too, bro!
What is this feeling
that I'm feeling?
Was this how Mokichi
must have felt?
‐Mokichi!
Well then?
Who's this Mokichi?
How's that?
You bastards!
You've got no complaints now!
Witness the work of the greatest
carpenters in the universe!
Wow!
That's amazing.
They even made a third floor, too.
But my room hasn't
changed at all!
What's the meaning of this?
Wow, you two are
really good carpenters.
All right, then!
Yeah.
We'll be going now.
Hey, what about my room, huh?
Well, there's still the exterior.
‐Exterior?
O‐Outside?
We already fixed the walls!
Yeah, you didn't say
anything about that before!
Hey, what about my room?
Don't you all ignore me!
No, but there's still something missing.
Something is missing...
The Odd Jobs was more...
More like this, I think.
Excuse me, that's far
beyond missing something!
That's a totally different building!
That's the Parthenon!
That's right.
Just like the "Pantihose".
You showed us that without
even knowing what the
‐Parthenon is?!
‐You have such bad taste!
It looked like this one!
This one!
That's the Castle in the Sky!
What is this?
You think we're genie
in a bottle?
That's impossible!
We're leaving!
All right, all right.
Okay, fine, just leave it as is.
Just make sure that it can fly.
Make it fly when you push
a button, you buttheads.
That's the biggest
problem so far!
In what world have you ever
seen a house that flies
when you push a button?
In the world of cartoons,
when you push a button,
everything works out somehow.
That's right.
All you do is just push a button.
I'm getting tired of this.
We're out of here.
Hey, did you ever hear
this story?
Damn it!
That young punk
is so annoying!
Plus, we already used up
all the money that Sakamoto
gave us a long time ago!
What a shock that Mokichi
had such a secret in his past!
Yeah, who can say no after
hearing that story, Bro!
Kaikei!
That must mean we have the same
craftsman's heart as Mokichi,
don't you think?
You think so, Bro?
We're exactly the same as him?
‐Mokichi!
Who the hell is this Mokichi?
Hey, Bro...
it's already morning.
Just a little bit more.
Wait, Bro?
Let's take a little break.
I'll go and get us some coffee, okay?
You can't do good work by
pushing yourself too hard.
Speed isn't everything, after all.
Yeah, but bro!
I'm sure that Mokichi had a cup of
coffee once in a while too...
as he sat back and appreciated his
marvelous work being completed.
While working, you reflect...
upon the joy that
your work gives you.
Isn't that what being a
craftsman is all about?
Oh, man, Bro!
I just got goosebumps
hearing you say that!
Kaikei!
We have but one goal,
haven't we?
‐Mokichi!
So...
Just who is this Mokichi?
Mokichi?
He doesn't exist at all.
I totally just made him up.
Are you serious, Gin?
Those two are so easy
to fool, Kagura.
Yeah but...
if they ever find out,
they'll be really mad at us.
I think it's best if we keep
it to ourselves.
Don't worry about it.
I mean, they're stupid enough
to buy that story.
I'm sure they'll
never figure it out.
You ass hole!
It was all a lie?!
Shit!
Hey, no, wait up!
What, Bro?
Are you serious?
You're saying Mokichi
never even existed?
That's right.
That's why we're leaving, Kaikei!
‐Our job is done here.
‐B‐But, But Bro!
Uh..
Hey, Gin...
Hah...
I'm never coming back to
this planet ever again!
But listen, Bro, is it okay
to just leave in the middle...
of what we were working on?
Who cares?
We worked hard for them and they
just played with our emotions.
They should be thankful
for what we do!
Those ungrateful bastards!
Oh, yeah?
You!
You've really got some
nerve showing your face
after everything you did.
Come on, don't say that.
There must be
some misunderstanding.
What?
Whether or not Mokichi existed
or not is not the point.
In fact, it's totally
completely irrelevant.
‐What do you mean?!
‐What are you talking about?
The real Mokichi...
lives inside the souls...
of craftsmen like you guys,
I can see in your eyes.
You guys are now starting
to look like a true Mokichi.
Y...You are...
Have you ever heard of this story?
I get it now!
Who knew there was such a mystery
hidden behind the story of Mokichi.
Mokichi, you're the best!
Who can say no after
hearing that story, Bro?
Kaikei!
I don't understand!
Did Mokichi really exist or not?
I don't understand any of this!
It doesn't matter, Bro!
Because it's all inside our souls.
It doesn't matter whether Mochiki
actually existed or not,
Mokichi lives inside our soul.
All right, Kaikei!
Let's do this.
Let's give it our all, buddy!
Let's show them that we are
the very best carpenters
in the entire universe, bro!
No way!
The second best!
Because the number one title
goes to the one and only...
‐Mokichi!
So just who the hell is
this Mokichi, damn it!
Good morning
I'm Thigh Bennington.
Today, here in Kabukicho,
Edo City's business and
shopping district,
we will be visiting the home of
Gintoki Sakata who
runs Odd Jobs.
Oh...
this must be his house...
Today's building,
the Sakata residence,
was recently renovated by
two Amanto architect brothers,
known as Unkei and Kaikei.
Their exterior is reminiscent
of the Greek Parthenon,
and it is combined with a gorgeous
palace section out of a fairy tale.
I will now guide you through
the Sakata residence.
Let's talk to the owner of
the house, Mr. Sakata.
Hello...? Hmm...
where's the doorbell?
Uh, let's see.
Is this it?
Just push the button...
I can feel a deep vibration,
as profound as the
exterior of the house.
What a wonderful house.
It can even fly!
Somebody go and get Mokichi.
Oh, what's wrong with me?
To have feelings for a girl...
other than Otsu...
Cat ears are...
Puuuuuuur‐fect!
The next episode..
It's a game where you
talk to a seaman
type unemployed
middle‐aged man
who is a DORK so you can
help him get a job.
Basically, even if you
start a conversation,
the DORK will ignore you.
That's because he already has his
hands full with his own life.
He'll get depressed sometimes.
You may want to give him
encouragement,
but you must not talk to him.
You must never say to him
"try your best."
Because he is already
trying his best.
Sometimes, he'll try to play with
a rope hanging from the ceiling.
When that happens, push the B
button repeatedly to cut the rope.
Sometimes, he may just stare
at the string hanging
from the light and say
"move rope...
move rope."
When that happens...
push the B button
repeatedly as well.
Sometimes, a strange woman
may pay him a visit.
When that happens,
just shout out loud, "Next!"
Very loudly.
In the end, the only word he
can say is "next!"