Is anybody home?
It's me, Katsura.
I guess nobody's here,
and they had to be gone
when its urgent.
Ex... excuse me.
Is Gintoki at home right now?
Well then, I'll just leave
these sweets here with you.
I hope you enjoy eating...
Well, it's not unlike her to disappear
for a couple of days,
but she's been missing
an entire week.
There's been no word from her,
and I've spoken to her friends,
but no one knows where she is.
Pull yourself together, Gintoki!
This is why I told you
not to drink too much.
Because I'm her father,
I am being humble,
but she's so beautiful
and attractive
that I'm worried she might
have gotten caught up
in something
unspeakably dreadful.
Yeah I'd say
there's a good chance
that she got caught up
in some sorta huge
ham processing machine
or something like that.
No, it's not like that.
I'm talking about
being caught up
in some sort
of criminal activity.
Criminal?
Oh, like unlicensed
ham processing?
Hey, you should stop
messing around.
Or are you trying to ruin
our chance to get this job?
But, are you sure you want us
to handle this?
Huh?
It sounds like something
better fit for the police.
I can't afford
a public scandal!
Our family is of an ancient
and honorable lineage
that has served the
Tokugawa Shogun family.
The entire clan will be
shamed if it gets out
that my precious darling daughter
is a club hopping skank.
Please, Odd Jobs, bring her back
home to me before word gets out.
Never seen anyone like her.
Someone told us that
she parties here all the time.
Maybe that's what someone
told you, young lady,
but you see, all Earthlings
look alike to me!
She got a name?
Um, it's... Ha... Hamilda!
Quit screwing around with me!
You obviously just made
that name up!
What kind of parent would give
their kid a name like that?
Why would I remember
her name?
Hey! Are you really
trying to find her?
Hey Gin, you know that
we'll never finish this job
if we leave it
all up to Kagura.
Man, whatever,
I don't care.
That ungrateful joke
of a daughter
is probably just camping out
at some dude's house.
This is so stupid.
Let's just give the father
some ham.
I honestly doubt that he'd ever
know the difference anyways.
There's no way he won't!
How long are you going to keep
milking that dumb ham joke!
Look, listen, I've got a "hamover"
and I feel like crap.
Just take care of it,
will ya, Shin? Thanks.
Hey, wait!
Gin, hey!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Young man, I suggest you learn
to pay a bit more attention.
Are you not embarrassed at all,
walking around with dust
on your shoulder?
You really oughta pay a bit more
attention to your appearance.
Now who the heck
was that guy?
Shinpachi!
I really can't be bothered, so I'm just
gonna bring this guy with us.
Oh my God, is anybody taking
this job seriously, damn it?
There's no way you can pass
this guy off as her!
That's not a "Hamilda."
Thats more like "Hamilton"!
Come on, ham are all the same,
you stupid piece of crap.
Is this your re‐deli‐ous phase?
Hamilton!
Hey, buddy, can you not waste
our screen time like this?
Hamilton, this is because
you drank so much.
This dude...
he's not drunk at all.
Hey, guys, guys,
don't bother with him.
I'll take it from here.
You two just go
enjoy yourselves.
Good grief.
The only thing anyone
ever thinks about
is smack, smack,
smack these days.
Smack, smack?
Did he get into a fight?
There's been a drug epidemic
going around in this place recently,
and it's real nasty stuff,
let me tell you.
Just say no, seriously.
I swear I'm never
drinking again.
Yeah, I know I always say that,
but this time, I mean it.
Who should I swear to?
I'll swear to that
hot weather forecaster.
Hey, I'm in here
taking a dump.
Give me the usual.
Huh?
I said hurry up
and give me the stuff!
I'm telling you, I can't go on
without it anymore!
Well...
You say that you want
the usual,
but it's a little more
watery than usual.
Stop screwing around
with me, idiot!
Am I not welcome now
that I'm broke, is that it?
Fine, just be that way!
I'll just go and talk
to the cops.
Hold on, wait a minute.
What the hell?
Talk to the cops?
Wait, hold on a second.
You can if you want,
but about what?
What do you mean?
Who the hell are you
talking to in there?
I told you to get the hell
out of my sight, bacon face!
The hell do you want?
Gin sure is taking long.
I've got a really bad feeling
about this place, you know.
We should leave here
as soon as we can.
I'll go and find him now.
I take it you're the scumbags
who've been snooping
around this place.
Wh... what's this all about?
Don't you play dumb with us.
You've been poking your noses
where they don't belong,
haven't you?
If you're so interested
in our business,
we'll show you
how frightening
the Harusame Space
Pirates can be!
Give it to me, hurry!
Give it to me!
Oh, poor Hammy!
‐Sorry for thinking you were just basic.
‐Please, I need it.
‐All the men to get mixed up with...
‐Please.
...it looks like you got caught
up with the worst of them all.
Daraku, it looks like we've got
a weird one here.
What should we do?
Hey, are you listening to me?
Damn it!
I Can't get it off.
What are you going
to do about this?
I just got this jacket tailored.
This is disgusting!
It's all sticky
and it won't come off!
Hey, there, Daraku,
are you listening...?
I told you to shut
the front door
while I'm attending
to my appearance!
If you've got a problem
with someone,
just get rid
of the problem.
Lets cut the crap
and get out of here!
There's a rerun of a show that
I really want to watch tonight.
Yeah, me too.
I'm not really the violent
misanthrope that I seem to be,
but there are three things
that I simply can't abide.
First are people who interfere
with my work.
Second, people who don't wash
their hands after using the bathroom.
And third, scuzzy looking people
with ugly mop tops.
And you are...
three for three!
I admit I'm honored.
And while we're sharing,
how about I tell you the three kinds
of people that I can't stand?
First, girls who get hysterical
while preparing for school festivals!
Second!
Desperate guys who pretend
to be excited about festivals
to try to connect
with those girls!
And third!
Hypocrite teachers who noddingly
embrace these previous idiots!
So then in other words, you just
really hate school festivals.
You must have had
a depressing adolescence.
Better than yours,
I'm sure of it.
Aren't you a little too old
to be sneaking a J in the John?
Although it seems
like you guys
are now into dealing
some serious poison.
Since you Sky People arrived,
there've been a lot more
dangerous things in the world.
Well, I can't have you pushing drugs
on our innocent children.
Pushing drugs?
That little pig is the one
who came running to me.
I just got her
what she asked for,
and then she starts
making a scene?
She's the one
causing me trouble.
Is that right?
Well I'm sorry this silly little girl
caused you trouble.
I'll take her home and
give her a good lecturing!
Oh, come on.
Are you all here
to take a leak or what?
There aren't enough toilets.
Hey, don't make this difficult!
Shinpachi! Kagura!
Hey! What're they doing?
You bastards!
What did you do to them?
You totally disgust me.
I got dirty again.
This thing is now ruined.
I'll just have to buy
a new one.
Hang in there, man!
I won't let you die on me.
I'm going to get you through this,
I promise. You'll see.
You really should just
get rid of that.
He ain't going
to make it, anyway.
You don't have what it takes
to rescue anyone, you know.
When have you ever managed
to protect anything
that matters to you?
All you do is lash out at
whatever's in front of you.
You slew them all,
and what did that leave you?
Nothing but a mountain
of corpses.
You're powerless.
Just get rid of it all.
Take the easy road.
There's nothing in this world
that you'll ever be able to protect!
It's unlike you to be
having a nightmare.
Were you dreaming about
the past just now?
Cobra?
What in the hell are you doing?
I remember!
Better not to strain yourself.
You're incapable of using
your left arm,
and I'm told that you've also
broken several ribs.
Your friend is doing
even worse.
She looks okay
on the outside,
because you thankfully
broke her fall.
But her body is rotting
from the inside out.
It's lucky you found her
before it got any worse
but it's unclear whether
she'll recover.
Oh, what a stupid kid.
So tell me, what were you doing
in a place like that?
Never mind that, tell me how
did you manage to save me?
And before that, apologize
for last time, you bastard.
Speaking of which...
are you at all familiar with this?
‐No.
‐It's an illegal substance...
...called "Paradise" that has been
going around all over the city lately.
It's made from a flower that
grows only on a remote planet,
and it's extremely addictive.
Everyone who uses it, without exception,
meets a very tragic end.
Us exclusionists have been gathering
information on the matter recently
in an attempt to rid the city
of Edo of this growing evil.
That's apparently where
you fell into all of this.
Who knows what
would've happened to you
if my men
hadn't found you.
So tell me, what were you doing
in a place like that?
More importantly,
who were all those guys anyway?
The Harusame Space Pirates.
They're the largest organized
crime syndicate in the Milky Way.
Their primary source of income
is their profits
from selling illicit drugs.
The very tips of their tentacles
have reached Earth,
and we can't rely
on the government police.
They're totally corrupted
by the Amanto,
so we hoped we could do
something on our own.
But these space pirates were able
to corner even you, Gintoki.
They seem to be
a formidable adversary.
We may have
underestimated them.
We might need
to rethink our strategies.
Hey, man,
are you even listening?
They kidnapped my friends,
and I can't just afford
to leave them there.
You really think you can
beat them in your condition?
"A man's life is like traveling a long
road with a load on his shoulders."
This is our family motto that we've
cherished for centuries, Cobra.
That is total bullshit!
It's the motto
of the Shogun family!
The first time I heard that motto,
I remember thinking of myself,
what a lame thing to say.
But what do you know?
That old guy had a point.
It's not really
a burden after all.
But everyone's got
both hands
full of something
that truly matters to them.
You just don't realize it
when you're carrying it.
It's only later you realize,
after it slips out of your hands.
How heavy it was to carry
in the first place...
so many times.
I thought I'd never carry
a load like that ever again.
And yet, before I realized it
I was carrying it again.
I'd feel so much better
if I got rid of it.
But I just can't bring
myself to do it.
Without those guys around,
I just can't enjoy life as much.
There's no point in arguing.
I still owe you that favor
from the bomb incident.
Let's go.
Huh?
You can't carry any baggage
with just one hand, can you?
For the time being,
I'll have to be your left arm.
Where is this place?
Where am I?
What am I doing right now?
Are these the idiots who were caught
snooping around and asking questions?
That's right.
They were becoming
a bit of a nuisance to us
so we set a trap
and they fell right into it.
I believe these are the exclusionist
rebels that hate the Amanto.
Ribbit, ribbit.
There was one other
odd samurai with them,
but we got rid of him along with
an annoying loud mouthed customer.
I warned you not to attract
too much attention.
There's a limit to how much we can
keep the government officials
under control and
looking the other way.
Of course, I understand.
We are only able to do business
thanks to your magnanimity, my lord.
So, how are you going to dispose
of these two pests?
I'll get the location of
their headquarters out of them
and destroy it.
I don't want them interfering
any further with our work.
I presume their leader is that man
named Katsura, I've heard about.
They're bunch of mad dogs, even
baring their teeth at the government.
Don't take them lightly.
Daraku, a moment please.
I'm sorry, there are some
weirdos outside.
Some weirdos outside?
I'll leave it up to you
to handle it.
I'm very busy right now.
I'm telling you again,
we don't need any crap like you!
Aw come on.
Can't you guys
just take us with you?
I mean, we want
to become pirates, too.
Ain't that right, Cobra?
My name's Captain Katsura
not Cobra.
You know, ever since we were
little punk ass kids,
we've always dreamed
of becoming pirates like you.
We wanna go out and search
for the lost treasure "One Punk."
Isn't that right, Cobra?
My name's Captain Katsura
not Cobra.
Never heard of this treasure.
Go find it yourselves.
Come on, don't be like that.
After all, my hand is a hook,
which means I can only be
a pirate or a coat hanger.
Not my problem.
I'm sure you can be
whatever you want to be.
Just go home!
This isn't a place
for the likes of you.
At the very least
you could give us an interview.
We even brought
our resumes with us.
Hey, are you awake now, kid?
Yeah, sleepy time's over, kid!
Oh, look at you.
You're so young.
It's such a shame
you got captured by pirates!
Oh, yeah, that's right, pirates.
I've been actually
kidnapped by pirates.
Kagura!
You know, I hate filthy people
and I hate filthy people who try
to interfere with my business.
It's about time I exterminate
all you filthy rats.
Tell me where your nest is.
If you try to hold out,
then she dies.
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me.
We know you're in league
with exclusionist rebels.
I said tell us where your base
of operations is!
Where is that scumbag Katsura?
What're you guys
talking about?
We're not exclusionist rebels
nor do we know
where Katsura is!
Let Kagura go, right now!
This is the land
of the samurai!
It's not your backyard!
The land of the Samurai,
you say?
There's no such thing
in this country anymore.
Kagura, no!
I don't want to get
in your way for this battle.
‐Bye‐bye.
‐Hold on!
Hold on!
Wait, wait, wait, wait...!
I've got you!
My wound just opened.
Is this where the interview
is being held?
Hi guys, I'm Gintoki SaKata,
and I'd like to try out
for captain, please.
My hobby is consuming sugar.
My special talent is being able
to sleep with my eyes open.
‐Gintoki!
You bastard,
you were still alive?
What the...?
Daraku, there was an explosion
in the storeroom!
Our Paradise!
And now my work here
is done,
which means that it's now
your turn, Gintoki!
Go ahead and
trash the place.
I'll take care of anybody
who gets in the way!
You're that damn Katsura!
You're wrong!
My name is Captain Katsura!
Look, it's Katsura!
Let's get him!
Off with Katsura's head!
You guys are in for it.
You've made an enemy of
the entire Harusame gang!
Soon, Harusame scattered
across the universe
will come here to kill you.
And so what?
You won't be around
to see it.
Listen...
I don't care what you do
somewhere else in the universe,
but anywhere within the reach
of my sword, is my country!
Anyone who comes here...
and messes with my people,
whether he's the Shogun, space pirates,
or an effin' meteorite,
I'll cut 'em all down!
Let's go!
Hey... you bastard...
you may not wash your hands
in the bathroom...
but your moves
are pretty clean.
Uh, I'm so beat,
everything's spinning.
I can't even walk.
Yeah, I'm feeling dizzy
from too much sun.
Carry me.
Why are you complaining,
you little brats?
Do you know who's
the most exhausted one here?
I fought my way over here
even though my body is a mess
and I have a hangover, too!
Both of us are feeling
pretty woozy too, you know!
That's right!
We're feeling woozy, boozy!
You know, I really
can't stand you guys.
I'm going home now.
Oh, come on,
knock it off already!
Okay, fine!
You want me to carry you?
I'll carry you!
What a miraculous recovery
they've made!
Gintoki, I feel like eating ramen.
I'm hungry.
Me too, but I'd be fine
with Sushi.
Don't be stupid!
Don't think we can go eat out
when its not your Birthday, man.
Oh, God, both of you guys
are heavy, dammit.
You better hold on,
and make sure you hold on
tightly this time.
Kimiko! Kimiko!
I'm so glad you're safe
and sound!
‐Kimiko!
‐Hey, old man.
You're hugging the wrong one!
Hey, I know how it is, pops.
There are some things in this world
you just don't want to see.
No, but isn't this happening
because he can see her?
This is Gintoki.
The other day, I was chasing after
a stray cat that stole my fish,
but I was naked and
everyone under the sun,
even a little dog,
was laughing at me
Anyway, the next episode...
Three episodes including
My name is Captain Katsura, not Cobra!
Believe it!
Did I get that right?