What's that?
You mean even Chat‐man and
Robby and the others were arrested?
Damn those Shinsengumi!
From what I've heard,
even Katsura and Takasugi
left Edo City
in order to escape
their pursuit.
Such cowards, all of them.
Have they forgotten
the Samurai spirit
that drives us
to save our country
without fearing any death?
Yes, but this may be
a good opportunity.
If we, The Three Scrooges
Brothers, act now,
we could surpass
Katsura and Takasugi,
and lead the Exclusionist Rebels.
They may be called
the special police,
but they're just a bunch of samurai
from the countryside.
If we take out their leader,
they'll be just a bunch of wandering
sheep without a shepherd.
‐Right!
Our first target is the brain
of Shinsengumi,
the demon vice‐chief,
Toshiro Hijikata.
‐Hey, Pops, give me the usual.
‐Okay.
Oh, this is the first time
I've seen you
without your uniform, Mr. Hijikata.
Today is my day off.
It's hard to find things to do
when you're single.
Better than having a wife
nag at you all day long.
‐Is that so?
‐I heard that, honey!
The demon vice‐chief
is totally off his guard.
It would be so easy
to get rid of him.
Shall we do it?
Here you go,
the Hijikata special!
What the hell is he eating?
It makes me sick
just watching him eat.
Here you are,
the Gintoki Sweet Bowl!
What?! Is that sweet
red beans on rice?
What kind of diner is this?!
Are there only weirdos here?!
Hey, hey, brother, excuse me.
You with the mayonnaise
over there,
could you do everyone
a favor and leave?
Seeing you slurping
that in your mouth
is gonna ruin our appetite.
‐Right, buddy?
‐What, me?
If that's the case, then I think
it would be best if you left.
Anyone with taste buds
so messed up
that they put sweet red beans
on rice has no right to eat at a diner.
‐Right, buddy?
‐Well, I...
Don't you know that since
the ancient times, it has been said
that carbohydrate go great
with sweets?
Like donuts and cakes.
Right, buddy?
I have no idea.
Don't you know that
the most sophisticated way
of enjoying the taste is
to have contradicting elements?
Adding salt or tartness
is the best way
to bring out
the original flavor.
In other words,
you need tons of mayo.
‐Right, buddy?
‐No, and stop asking me.
I don't want to be part of this.
Don't compare my Gintoki Sweet Bowl
to your dog food.
This is a historic dish created
by General Sandwich,
who was too lazy to eat
rice and dessert separately.
‐Right, buddy?
‐Who is that?
And wouldn't General Sandwich
be inventing sandwiches?
‐What's with the rice?
‐Oh, yeah?
Well, mine was created
by General Barbarossa
who grew tired of eating rice
and mayonnaise separately
and created...
Who the hell are those Generals?!
And mayo isn't
some essential nutrient
you have to have
with every meal!
All right then,
let's compare them
to see which tastes better,
the Gintoki Sweet Bowl
or your dog food special.
‐Right, buddy?
‐What do you mean, "buddy"?
‐Hold it!
‐Well, bring it on.
‐Right, buddy?
‐Wait, hold on, it's not right!
What is this?!
Why should I have to eat it?
Oh, no!
We need an objective opinion.
That's why it has to be done
by a complete stranger, right, dummy?
Yeah, we're counting on you.
Right, dummy?
You just called me dummy!
Is that a way to ask a favor?
How is it, dummy?
Isn't mine a lot tastier?
Right dummy?
Hey, dummy!
Thank you very much.
Damn it, we didn't anticipate
such interference.
Big Brother, who was
that silver‐haired guy?
No idea.
Never mind, Jiro.
It's your turn now.
Don't blow it.
How annoying!
Why did I have to run into that jerk
of all people on my day off?
I was thinking
of catching a movie,
but it's for children.
I don't feel like watching it.
Oh, Pedro, help me!
My younger sister,
Oshizu, is lost,
and she must be crying
by herself somewhere.
Please help me, Pedro!
Why don't you try
calling the cops?
Please help, Pedro!
Listen, they cut my phone off.
You're just like all the rest.
You only come asking, " Pedro, Pedro"
whenever you need help.
The other day,
you rang my doorbell...
It's really getting to me.
This kid movie captures
the heart of adults, too.
It's a movie all adults should see.
Just what scene
is he crying over?
But this darkness
will make my job easier.
Just one blow
right from behind.
Hey, you over there!
Your sobbing is way too loud.
I couldn't hear a thing.
What did Pedro just say?
What about ringing his doorbell?
I'm sorry. The girl rang
Pedro's doorbell and...
You again!
What's with you, man?
Why are you showing up
everywhere I go?
You just stole my line, stupid!
What? Are you that desperate
to make a friend?
You wanna be friends?
You idiot!
I was wondering who the hell
was the annoying guy
munching on popcorn behind me!
Get out!
‐Get out now!
‐Shut up!
I was just trying to get
the popcorn kernel
that got stuck behind my teeth!
Now you've made me
lose track of the whole story!
I don't know what the hell
is going on anymore!
The popcorn is the only thing
I've got now!
That's what happens when a
samurai eats such frivolous foods.
Are you an idiot or something?
You popcorn head!
I think your brain
just popped out, didn't it?!
I don't want to hear that
from a mayo samurai!
How do you set that
slicked‐down hair of yours?!
With a glob of mayonnaise
or something, huh?
Why don't you step outside!
What offering do you want me
to put on your grave?
Sweet beans? Popcorns?
What do you say?!
‐That hurts!
‐Hey! Keep it down, you guys!
If you're gonna fight,
take it outside.
You're bothering people!
Yeah, I can't see!
What's the matter
with you, losers?
Watching this crappy movie
in middle of the day.
"Go to work, lazy bums!"
Says the guy
with the braided hat.
"I'm so pissed off.
Come up here and fight!"
Says the guy
with the braided hat.
Wait, no!
Why would I...
All right!
You wanna fight?
Let's get him!
Go him!
What?!
Just a minute!
Now's my chance.
If I can use this racket
to finish him off.
Hey, everyone!
Let's be quiet
when watching the movie.
This movie makes me cry.
Damn that Hijikata
and that silver‐haired guy.
I'll get them for sure next time.
I will avenge my brothers.
Why do I have to be
so exhausted on my day off?
Everywhere I go,
I run into that jerk.
I hate to admit it, but it seems
the two of us think alike.
Hey, I feel like taking a hot bath
and a nap in a massage chair,
but I won't be tricked.
The fact that I'm thinking this now
means he's probably thinking
the exact same thing.
So should I just do the opposite
and go where he
doesn't want to go?
But he's probably
thinking that too,
so today, I used reverse psychology
and headed straight
for the Spa Land.
He must be thinking, "Wait!
Is this a diary
or something?"
So I'll do the opposite
of the opposite!
Hii‐jii‐ka‐taaaaaa!
Cut it out already.
I thought you'd show up again
at the place
where I wanted to go,
so I thought of going
where I didn't want to go,
but then I didn't like
the idea of going
where I don't want
to go because of you,
so I'll be true to myself today
and then, I thought, "Wait!
Is this a diary or something?"
So I ended up here.
Dammit. Only the "Wait,
is this a diary?" part matched.
I was a fool to try to read
your mind too deeply!
Well, never mind.
It must be some kind of fate
that we keep meeting like this.
So get outta here.
Why on earth do I have
to take orders from you?
If someone's leaving,
it should be you.
Hey, hey, are you
in elementary school?
If we keep meeting like this,
we'll get into a fight,
so it'd be best if we don't
see each other at all.
It's my very mature opinion.
So you should be
the one to leave.
Hey now, don't you say that!
I was actually
thinking of leaving,
but if I leave
after you tell me to,
then it's as though I'm
following your orders!
Now I can't leave!
Consider my feelings.
Shut up!
You're the brat!
Let me make this clear.
I'm not leaving until you do.
Who are you kidding?!
I'm not leaving either.
Their stupidity is so alike.
‐Never mind. Just get out.
‐ You can both keep on arguing in there.
I'll wrap a chain
and put on a sign here.
And you two
can just shrivel up!
Hey, enough already.
You're drenched with sweat.
You'll collapse from dehydration.
I'm doing just fine, though.
You think you're so tough, huh?
I can see your smile twitching.
I can see it in your eyes,
you're screaming for water.
Though I'm doing just fine.
Hey, I'm much more okay
than you are, huh?
No way, my okay is much more
thorough than your okay.
That's what you say, but I know
you're actually suffocating.
I can see right
through you, man.
Don't be ridiculous.
I love saunas,
I love to steam.
In fact, the other day,
I got a little carried away
and steamed buns for
Shinpachi and Kagura.
Shall I raise
the temperature in here?
I like it hotter, you see.
What?!
He raised the temperature
even higher!
Not enough steam!
Pour the entire bucket in.
Are you guys stupid or something?
You're sealed in there, you know!
You can't get out!
It's such a Paradise!
I can feel my adrenaline surge!
Now, you're ready
to take off to Paradise.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
It's about time you're gonna
lose your conscience.
Give it up, you.
Just so you know,
I'm not giving up.
‐Never!
‐Hey!
Who do you think
you're talking to?!
Who the hell
are you talking to?!
Looks like you've reached
your limit.
‐This cigarette has no flavor at all.
‐Wait wait!
That's not a cigarette!
Seriously, man, you should
just give up already.
What? What is it with you?
You plan on dying in here?
Because of your stupid stubbornness?
Oh, even a guy like you
would have people
who would mourn your death!
If you still won't give up,
it's just your ego!
You're an idiot, you know!
For your own sake,
give it up!
Please.
I'll give you three bucks.
Who would give up
for just three bucks?
They are such fools.
So why... why am I...?
Why am I so moved
by these fools?
We samurai of the Exclusionist Rebels
risk our lives for our country.
These men who can put their lives
on the line for something this stupid.
Maybe we aren't so different.
Hey.
Man, you really are
a piece of work.
I have to say...
I give up.
Looks like you win this match.
Hey!
S‐Sorry, but could you take
a message to Odd Jobs?
Tell them bye‐bye.
You bastard.
I don't like taking messages.
Go tell them yourself.
I can't do it.
I can't kill such courageous men.
I just can't.
Hey, come out of there,
you morons!
‐What?
‐I was just kidding, sucker!
What?!
I told you I can read
you like a book!
Oh, damn, let's call it even.
No way, you totally got
out first, it's not even!
No, you got out first, moron!
Wait. Who is this guy?
I found you, Kagura!
Yo!
‐Get a hold of yourself, Yo!
‐Hey, you dummy!
The rule is no kicking if one of us
is within one meter of the can!
I have never heard
of such a wimpy rule.
Oh, forget it!
She doesn't know
how to hold back at all!
I'm sick of this too.
You take this way
to seriously, dummy!
We won't play games
with you anymore.
Idiot!
Moron!
‐Let's go.
‐What a bunch of wimps.
Giving everything you've got
is what makes a game fun.
Very well said.
That's exactly right.
Because when you give your best,
your performance level
will go above your abilities.
If you try as hard as you can
at everything you do,
even boring things will be fun.
Everything in the world
is just one big game.
Little girl, how about it?
Want to play
"kick the can" with me?
Well Gin always says I shouldn't
play with guys I don't know.
But it's okay if it's
an old guy you don't know?
No, because all men
are beasts.
You're young,
but very street smart.
I like you even more.
Then how about we ask
your folks to join us, eh?
Don't treat me like a kid,
you old fart!
Hey, isn't that Kagura over there?
Yeah, there she is.
Hey!
I was so shocked.
He seemed so healthy
just a while ago.
He suddenly collapsed
two nights ago.
We were surprised, but I think
that he was even more surprised by it.
So true.
None of us know what tomorrow
will bring, that's for sure.
Please don't let this
depress you too much, Zen.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Man, this is such a drag.
Why do I have go through all
these suffocating formalities
for my crappy old man?
‐Kick the can?
‐Yeah.
The old fart wants us
all to play together.
Let's do it.
What are you saying?
I told you over and over
until my tongue shriveled up
to not talk or play with strangers.
You're a fool.
Do you want to get kidnapped?
I'm not a stranger,
I'm just a strange old man!
Be quiet.
Men are all beasts, let's go.
Better an old woman you know
than an old man you don't know.
She's treating us
to barbecue,
and that doesn't happen
too often.
In times like this,
old ladies are far better.
Old ladies are awesome!
Heart‐Warming, almighty.
Granny, in short...
she is a...
That spells "HAG", you idiot!
Hey!
I'll be the it,
so let's just play!
Just kick the can!
I told you we're not playing...
‐...you old fart!
‐Hey, leave him alone!
Do you want me to kick it?
I'll kick it for ya!
Bring that back
within twenty seconds,
and we'll play with you,
you old fart.
You're evil, pure evil!
Catherine, you shouldn't
bully the elderly!
Shut up, I've got to eat.
I'm having a craving
for protein.
Come on, let's go before
the old hag changes her mind!
Catherine, get lost
and watch the shop.
If you can't be nice
to the elderly,
then don't expect the elderly
to be nice to you.
What are you saying?
You're not an elderly,
Miss Otose.
You're still so young
and energetic!
Okay, I got the can!
Let's start the game!
It's a pity we lost
such a great man.
Even the most formidable warrior
of the Spy Agent
could not defeat old age.
What are you talking about?
He was nothing more than a
good‐for‐nothing old pervert
who was playing around
all year long.
You don't know how much
trouble he caused me.
No, no, no mere pervert
could be a great master
of the ninja school.
All of the renowned ninja
in Edo City these days
were brought up and
trained by your father.
You may call him
a good‐for‐nothing,
but I loved that
mischievous side of him.
Master!
I got here as fast as I could
when I heard
he was in critical condition.
Dad has already died.
‐The critical state was two nights ago.
‐What?
That can't be!
Master!
Damn the critical condition!!
Hey, the guy being bent
in half under your feet
seems to be
in critical condition too.
He's in a V‐shape.
Just get it over with already!
I just love this tension.
I feel like I'm a little kid again.
Are you ready, boys and girls?!
Here comes the old man!
Where are you headed?
To the afterlife?
Man, why do we have
to play kick the can
with an old geezer
we don't even know?
All I wanted was
to eat barbecue.
I'm starving for meat.
I'm sorry for the old man,
but I'll just let myself
get caught
so we can end
this game quickly.
How dare you say
such a thing?!
You're choosing to lose
without even trying?
You call yourself a soldier?
We call whimpy people
like you losers!
Sergeant, refer this loser
to the court‐martial?
Stop your yapping,
Private Chihuahua.
If we have to play,
then we're not gonna lose.
Barbecue tastes way better after
a win than a defeat, Sergeant.
You said it right,
Private Chihuahua.
Kick the can
is just a kid's game.
You win if you topple that can
before you're spotted by "It".
You need a strategy to knock it over
without being detected.
With that in mind,
get ready to fire.
Aye, aye, sir!
Is that what you call
kick the can, Sergeant?
It's kick the can
in its purest form.
Remember your childhood days.
How you cried when
the wind toppled the can over
and all the captives were freed.
It's basically the same thing.
No way, man! You can't throw,
that's cheating!
You're way too soft, loser!
The whole joy of kick the can
is to knock the can over
in the dirtiest way possible
and enjoy in a devilish way
watching "It" cry in despair!
It's all over if you
end up as "It"!
I don't know how many times
the can got knocked over,
and how many times I cried
as I pretended to count to 100
while everyone else hid from me.
It's a game
of triumph and tears.
That's kick the can!
Hey, guys!
This isn't kick the can,
it's murder!
It's pure murder, you guys!
Private Chihuahua!
Who ordered you
to hit the old man?
Sergeant!
With all due respect sir,
but that grenade
was thrown by you!
This is a matter
for the court‐martial!
We'll all be sued!
You've literally killed him!!
Wait a minute!
Up we go now.
He got up
like nothing happened!
Damn it!
Why don't you die, old man?!
You're not playing
kick the can anymore!
He's guarding the can
with his cane!
‐Damn it!
‐How is he moving like that?
I found you.
There you are.
‐Yikes!
‐Ninja knives!
What? Who is he?
What? Kick the can?
Oh, have you forgotten, Sacchan?
We played it a lot
in Master's class.
Kick the can demanded
the ability to hide yourself
and make instantaneous decisions.
It's similar to our spy work.
So as part of our ninja training,
we played kick the can
quite a bit, remember?
Oh, yes, we did.
That's right.
Now that you mention it.
It was really fun.
If you can't remember,
don't pretend like you do, okay?
And why did you come to the funeral
dressed like that?
I thought tonight was the crucial night
so I dressed up for the occasion.
I thought we could all
go for a drive
after Master got through
the critical condition.
That outfit was for critical condition?
Anyway, I can't forget
the smile on Master's face
whenever he played
kick the can.
I think he had more fun
playing than we did.
He really was like a big kid.
I'm sure that's why
all the kids loved him.
You guys compliment him
far too much.
You're wasting your time!
Did you think you could
beat me with your legs?
Found you, four‐eyes!
You fell for my trap.
A classic error
in kick the can...
over pursuing one target!
‐Dang!
‐That can is wide open!
I scraped my head!
My head's been grated!!
You fools!
Found you too, Silver Hair!
‐Shinpachi!
‐Here! I got it!
Goooo!
I'm gonna get the can!
Over my dead body!
Found you, four‐eyes
and silver hair.
I stepped on the can.
My father loved
playing kick the can.
When I was little we often
played it together,
and I always thought
"what a great father he was."
I was also worried
it might interfere with his job,
because he played
with me so much.
I was very much grateful
when I was a kid.
But even after I became an adult,
he still asked me to play.
So I realized "Wait a minute!
I thought he was playing
for my sake,
but he was playing
for his own sake."
Really, it's like he went straight
from being a kid
to being an old man.
He was always having fun,
which used to annoy me
when I was a teenager,
but I also envied him
on the other hand.
Kagura, I found you!
It's rather easy for kids
to become adults,
but it's not so easy for adults
to keep the spirit of a kid,
where you can enjoy everything.
And for that,
yes, I admire him.
There is just one thing, however,
that I can never forgive.
That bastard sold all my comics
to a used book store
and bought a shit‐load
of porno DVDs!
That makes me so angry!
Oh, forgive me for losing it.
But it still makes me angry,
and brings tears.
I've said many things,
but in summary,
he was a crappy father.
That's how he always was,
so don't be surprised if
he comes to visit you as a ghost.
If he does, please play
kick the can with him.
What is it?
Well, I thought I just
saw him smile a little bit.
What are you talking about?
He's always had
a smiley face.
It always annoyed me.
Next episode...