Uh, since all of you
are graduating,
today is your last class.
Kabukicho, the Town of Greed,
a town where one can find
all kinds of pleasure,
drinks, women and drugs.
There's nothing
you can't get in this town.
And tonight, these men
are about to seek challenges
on a whole new stage.
‐Are you ready for this?
‐Yeah.
Tonight we're saying goodbye
to our dead broke jobless lives.
We're gonna win.
Everything there is to be won!
That's right!
I'm gonna win
more tons of easy money
than I could ever spend
in my entire life!
And we'll celebrate with Dom Perignon
mixed with Dom Perignon!
We'll drink until
we get diarrhea!
‐Casino, here we come!
Is everyone ready
to place bets?
Odd or even?!
Place your bets now!
Even!
Odd!
‐Even!
Well, thank God
it isn't winter at least.
We'd be freezing to death.
That's true, but our wallets
just went into hibernation.
I think we have God on our side.
We sure do.
The God of Poverty
is definitely with us.
Now that I think about it,
my left shoulder's been feeling
awfully heavy lately.
Like there's someone on it.
Like the God of Poverty.
Don't you think?
My left shoulder's
drooping a bit.
You worry too much.
Luck won't come near you
if you always look so glum.
Lately I keep seeing
this creepy old man
in a cloak carrying
a huge scythe.
But I've decided
not to worry about him.
That I really think
you should worry about.
Speaking of the devil,
look behind you.
Behind you.
Unwanted spirits
and entities, leave now!
Eloim, Essaim,
frugativi et appelavi!
Talking about whether God
is on your side or not.
And you call yourselves gamblers?
These are...
the clothes they won off us!
But... who are you?
Luck is not something
that's served in a restaurant.
You can't simply wait
for the luck to come to you.
You have to seduce
the goddess of gambling yourself.
He's amazing!
He just keeps winning
since he came here!
Hey, do you see
that scar on his face?
Could he actually be Kanbei,
the Luck Reader?
"The Luck reader"?
The unbeatable gambler
with amazing luck.
He's a legend!
They say he can read
how his luck's gonna run.
He can change
all odds in his favor.
He's like an idol
to every gambler.
I heard he disappeared
from Edo City for a while,
but I never thought
I'd get a chance to see him!
Noooo!
Well, however legendary
this guy may be,
I didn't know the Goddess
of Gambling was such a tramp.
Hell, I've been working
my ass off to seduce her
and she won't even
look at me.
She's probably not interested
in married guys.
My wife left me ages ago
so I'm practically single right now.
I'm hoping Lady Luck would have
a one night stand with me.
Maybe the goddess likes
the wild type, just like him.
Yeah, I bet she does.
You're right!
We can be wild too!
Odd or even?
‐Even!
Come on, what was wrong?
Maybe we don't look
wild enough.
Maybe if we tried
to get more of
"I don't give a damn"
kind of look.
Hasegawa, take off your boxers.
Hey, I don't mind, but I'm not
exactly wild down there.
It's more on the mild side.
What are you morons doing?
And after everything I went through
to get your clothes back for you!
Are you stupid?
Go home already!
You're clearly not suited
for gambling!
You did that all by yourself.
We never asked you to!
Looking wild but showing
kindness once in a while.
Is that the secret to winning the heart
of the Goddess of gambling?
You're so full of it.
Careful not to catch a cold.
Adding superficial kind
words won't work!
There are two types
of gamblers.
The first type are guys
who love to gamble.
The second type are guys
who think they're cool
when they gamble,
and the second type
makes crazy bets.
He gets caught up
in his own euphoria
and he destroys himself,
but the very best gamblers
place their bet when
they are really sure.
They don't go crossing bridges
unless they're sure
the bridge won't break.
You guys are obviously
the second type.
Just take my advice and
quit gambling right now.
We're not the second type.
We're the third.
There's no such thing.
Sure, there is.
The type who is desperate
for money the easiest way.
So go get a job!
You'll never understand the feeling
of being working class like us.
Gamblers are just fooling
around with luck.
You're wrong there.
Life itself is like a big gamble.
So we are all gamblers.
Just shut up.
Anyway, seeing two guys
in a pair of boxers
in this sacred gambling
den is disturbing me.
I won't allow you to foul
this place any further.
What a strange guy.
What?
How did this happen to me?
My God, where did I
go wrong?
Hey, hey.
Are you allowed to foul the sacred
gambling den with your loincloth?
‐It's you guys!
‐Hey!
On top of that, you disgraced
your name by cheating.
What do you think, Hasegawa?
Trying to seduce Goddess
of Gambling with magic tricks?
How pitiful.
Totally pitiful.
And you're juxtaposed
to be a legendary gambler!
I already told you that
you have to create your own luck!
Hey, your cool dude act
won't work anymore.
Just look at yourself!
Well, you guys certainly have
some powerful bad luck.
It' s obvious that you took away
all of my good luck with it.
Oh, c'mon, all we ask
is you do us a favor.
Blast away all this bad luck
with your little tricks and
help us to make some money
and we won't say a word!
Gentlemen.
We would like you to
please come along with us.
Man, the God of poverty is,
he's always with us.
So, these are the scumbags
who tried to cheat
in my gambling den.
You have quite the nerve.
Did you really think
you can outwit me,
one of the Elite Four
of Kabukicho,
Kada, the Princess Peacock herself?
So are you three
prepared to die?
Hold it!
We didn't chea...!
I hate men who make excuses!
And you call yourself a gambler?
Hey, hey.
What a scary goddess
this one is!
She's the female leopard who controls
most of the casinos in Kabukicho.
No one who messes in her territory
has ever made it out alive.
We're doomed to end up
at the bottom of the ocean.
I thought I recognized your face.
You are Kanbéi,
the one they call
"the Luck Reader."
So the legendary gambler
of Edo City
turned out to be
just a cheater?
I heard of your name
even on my planet.
A man who could read and change
his luck even in the worst situations.
That was a long time ago.
Now, my luck reading
eye has closed,
and I can't read anything.
I am only a cheater now.
So you could see luck with
that closed right eye of yours.
Interesting.
Rumors say five years ago,
you lost your right eye
after losing in a big gambling match.
Surely, you can see
with your left eye
what you used to be able
to see with your right eye.
And so, I shall give you
one last chance.
This is...
It seems that our life depends
on playing a game of Mah‐jong.
Playing Mah‐jong?
Isn't this kinda wrong,
showing Mah‐jong...
in a wholesome samurai show?
Shouldn't we be playing games
like twister or jenga?
Well, I'm sure it has to do
with grown up matters
like sponsors and things.
Mah‐jong, huh?
But I only know the basic rules.
H‐Hasegawa, you...
you are...
What is it?
Is there something on me?
What is this?!
What's this?
Why only me?!
It's you!
You know him?
He's Akagé, the mah‐jong wizard,
member of the Kada Gang.
He's been playing for 20 years
and hasn't lost once.
Powerful players called Dragon
and Tigers and whatever
were all no match for him.
He's a living legend
in the underworld.
He has no equal.
Well I must say,
it is an honor to meet
the legendary Kanbéi,
the Luck Reader.
Let's all enjoy tonight.
So this means, if we beat you,
we can leave this place alive?
That's right.
If even just one
of you beats me...
all three of you can go free.
But if you lose...
you'll become fish food
in the bay of Edo City!
This is ridiculous.
Well, we have no choice
but to go along.
There's no other way
to get out of here alive.
But still, what the hell
is that woman thinking?
I hear that she really
loves gambling too.
I'm sure she's planning
to enjoy watching us squirm.
What a detestable woman!
All right then,
shall we begin?
This is a battle to the death!
Six to the right.
Well, that means
you're the dealer.
What did you just say?
Calling me a dealer?
Mommy doesn't remember
raising a drug dealer!
This guy's eyes and his moves.
It's obvious that
he's no ordinary guy.
Gin and I are the types who'll never
be loved by the Goddess of Gambling.
The Luck Reader
is our only chance!
What?
Not again.
What's with these crappy tiles?
What will I do?!
There's no way
I can win with this!
That's why I didn't want to play.
This really sucks!
Man, we just started and he's already
talking like it's hopeless.
‐This really sucks!
‐All right then.
I guess it starts with me!
‐Take that!
‐Hey, you can't do that!
You can't just discard
three tiles like that.
I can't? So what?
What do I do?
I don't need them anyway.
It's over.
He doesn't even know the rules.
Help, someone!
Please help us!
You've got to be kidding me!
To think that such amateurs
are trying to challenge me?
That's fine,
I'll go easy on you
and let you bend the rules,
let's keep going.
This is impossible,
I tell you.
A team of three beginners
is no match
against a great
mahjong wizard like you.
Hey, hey, what's the matter,
Hasegawa?
The match has just started, after all.
Akagé is being so kind to us,
so it's too early
to throw in the towel.
Absolutely.
Gambling is never over
until the very, very end.
And I'm going to play
to win, my way!
Where does his confidence
come from?
But his eyes look so sure.
Maybe a miracle will happen.
I win!
It's Little Dragons, Half Flush,
12 thousand points!
I knew it was hopeless!!
We don't stand a chance!
I was a fool to even think that
we had a chance for a second!
Now, now, don't get too dismayed.
This is just one game we lost.
There are more.
That's right.
We still have the Luck Reader
on our side.
The man with amazing luck
who can turn the tide!
I win!
It's Pure Outside Hand Three colors,
12 thousand points!
Aww, come on!
We can't win!
We will never win!
Pong! Chow!
I win!
Kong! It's a Reach!
It's a draw!
It's All Simples, All Runs,
Three Colors,
Dora Dora, 12 thousand points!
It's over.
Each of you has zero points.
It's called Hakoten, meaning you have
nothing to bet anymore.
Hakoten or "one to ten,"
I don't care!
A man's worth is not determined
by how many points he has!
No? Then, what will you do?
Well, I'm not letting you
win the next game, honey!
Play strip mah‐jong?!
The godfather used to say,
"a man who doesn't
take off his shirt
can never be a real man."
He never said that!
Sounds like fun.
Alright, fine, let's play
another round.
We'll play again.
The most important thing
for a gambler to have is guts.
And he certainly seems
to have that.
But it's never
really that easy, is it?
You can't just win
by having guts.
Calm down, you guys.
After all, one must never lose
his cool when gambling.
Even if you are
surrounded in flames,
you must always
keep a cool mind.
I'm cold already.
In fact, my mind and body
are both freezing!
Well now, it seems you have
nothing else to strip then.
It is game over.
How boring this was.
I thought I could enjoy
this a bit longer.
To think, a legendary man
known as the Luck Reader
could be this weak.
Playtime is over, gentlemen.
Now I am taking your lives.
Sorry, but it's the end
of the line for you.
He's the legendary Wizard,
after all.
He's way above us.
This is the end of us.
Listen, pops.
I wanted to ask you
just one little thing.
When your right eye was good,
were you really able
to see luck?
Well he probably cheated
that for all I know.
Don't you worry.
I'll take over
that legend from tonight.
You shut up!
Just shut up and be quiet!
If I could see luck,
I wouldn't be one‐eyed today.
Kanbéi, your little friend has
caused some real trouble for us.
How are you going
to settle this?!
There is only but one thing
I can say.
I just remembered.
I hear you have a pretty
interesting right eye, Kanbéi.
I heard it can read luck.
I have always made
choices in my life
that I won't regret later on.
If you want him to live,
cut out your right eye!
I have always done
exactly as I wanted
in gambling and in real life.
And this is how you ended up?
In the end, you're not as much
of a man as they say you are.
And trust me I'll prove it
to you right now!
They're mine!
Now I'll stop their breathing.
It's a reach!
‐I win!
‐What?
I said I win!
It's Seven Pairs!
Damn right, he won!
what, but how?
How can you?
I thought you didn't
even know the rules!
No, I really don't.
That's why I played
however I wanted to.
I didn't know I had
a winning hand until just now.
Besides, I really don't like you.
As long as you don't beat me,
I don't give a damn
about the rest.
That's utterly insane!
Wh‐what, but how?
How can you?
I thought you didn't
even know the rules!
No, I really don't.
That's why I played
however I wanted to.
I didn't know I had
a winning hand until just now.
Besides, I really don't like you.
As long as you don't beat me,
I don't give a damn
about the rest.
That's utterly insane!
He really is insane for sure,
but it looks like lady luck
is on our side now.
Let's do it, pops!
‐It is payback time!
Reach, All Simples, All Runs,
Dora Dora Dragon Punch!
East, South, West, North!
King's Tile Draw!!
Excessive tiles!
Lack of tiles!
Foul! Peeping!
Rule Breakers!
‐Double East, Double South...
‐Double Reach Kick!!
We're no small fries!
So don't mess with us!
Now we're all naked.
So let's settle it
with the next game.
I can't lose to these guys.
Princess Peacock won't abide losers.
If I lose now,
I'll be killed.
I'll do whatever it takes to win.
Whatever it takes!
Well, I guess
I underestimated you guys.
But this is it.
I'll finish you off
with this one deal.
I'll send both, you and
Kanbéi straight to hell!
I know that I can't win
by playing fair...
but I still have
my final weapon.
Sorry, but you're gonna
have to disappear!
Lethal weapon!
Giant Tiger Illusion Tiles!
I can shuffle
1,000 tiles per second!
There's no way
you can see my moves!
Oh, sorry...
I was sitting for so long,
my legs were starting to hurt.
It wasn't on purpose, really.
Oh man, what a mess this is.
Let's put the tiles back.
I'll help you.
Stop it!
Never mind.
Damn it.
Some of my tiles
ended up in the wrong position.
Especially that row
that the sunglass guy piled.
I have to get it back!
It's all right.
It might take time,
but it's no problem.
Here I come!
Well, bring it on!
What is this called?
Hey, I just... well...
I'm the dealer,
so I was about to discard
one tile and look!
It seems like I win!
See... It's only "all runs" but...
It doesn't matter
what hand it is.
You have a winning tile
from the beginning!
Heavenly hand?
Good fortune bestowed
upon man by Heaven!
Heavenly hand?
Impossible!
How can that possibly be?!
So finally, in the end,
the Goddess of Gambling
decided to have a one
night stand with me!
You did it, Hasegawa!
I always knew you had it
in you all along!
How could this have happened?!
Where did I go wrong?
I don't understand
where I went wrong.
...will keep loving me forever.
That's life for you, isn't it?
Say Gin, let's go celebrate
before the Goddess of
Gambling turns away from me.
That sounds good.
How about we splurge
on some Dom Perignon
mixed with Dom Perignon?
Take it easy, you guys.
You useless bastard!
Well then, that's why gambling is...
What happened?
You all flunked the grade.
Come back to class next year!
Everyone repeats the grade!