The wife's name is Sacchan.
And the husband's name is Gintoki.
Come again?
They were two ordinary people,
‐who had an ordinary romance,
‐Hey!
‐and a perfectly ordinary marriage...
‐Stop making up your own recollection
‐of the past episode, listen!
‐But one thing was different...
‐You're not, even in this episode.
‐the wife Sacchan was a masochist.
Hey!
Is that your punchline?
Whoa!
Look here!
Congratulations, because you
have won first prize!
Yes, you have!
Enjoy the ultimate vacation
of your a lifetime dreams...
by flying into outer space.
Come and join the adventure...
where you'll experience a world
you've never seen before.
You, too, can experience the
space travel of your dreams.
‐Hey, Gintoki.
Don't you want to go to outer space,
‐at least once in your lifetime?
What are you talking about, man?
There's no air in outer space, you know?
If there's no air, then you'll,
you know, die or something.
Oh, welcome back, Kagura.
Hey, come on, what's this about?
Are you in your rebellious phase, Kagura?
Do you want us to change
your diapers for you?
Kneel before me,
worthless peasants!
I tell you, show me some respect!
You worthless samurai!
Call me "Madame Foreman"!
Wouldn't "Princess queen"
be better, Madame Foreman?
A foreman is more productive
than a Princess queen
and therefore more important!
In fact, call me Madame Slim
and Slender Foreman!
Madame Foreman, did you get
the toilet paper for us?
I forgot to get the butt wiping paper,
but I did get a much better
piece of paper.
A paper that lets us fly!
A trip through outer space,
for up to three people?
Madame Foreman!
‐Hooray!
All passengers with tickets
for space travel.
Come on, now.
I don't have anything metal on me.
Are these things so sensitive they
respond to people's iron wills now?
There has been an influx in crimes
perpetrated by the Exclusionist Rebels
recently, so please go through again.
Oh, I know what that is!
I forgot about the two balls of steel
I have in between my legs, lady.
Listen, sir, please kindly shut the hell
up, or I'll smash your pretty face in.
All passengers with
tickets for space travel,
‐please go through security at this time.
‐ wish I could've brought
my sister along with me.
The view of Earth from space
must be so beautiful, right Kagura?
Listen, miss
bringing pets aboard is
strictly prohibited.
But it's not a pet.
It's a hat.
Miss, I'm afraid hats don't pant.
What's that?
It's not a hat!
It's a humidifier.
Your humidifier smells like
rotten meat!
Fine, it's a pet.
Sadaharu won't cause
anyone any trouble,
and he doesn't bite at all, not ever.
I guarantee it.
What's that?
He's doing it now!
He's doing it as we speak!
Hey, sir!
Are you all right?
What's this?
I was having such a nice little nap.
Oh, is it already time for the flight?
Wow, my head is really throbbing.
I guess I drank too much yesterday.
No, it's not because of what
you had yesterday
rather, it's because of what
is having you right now.
Wow, I'm totally drenched in sweat.
It's bright red.
It must be because
I had tomato juice.
Hey come on!
There's a limit to how positive
a person can be!
I feel really heavy.
This is definitely a hangover.
Hey, sir!
Are you listening to
what I'm saying?
Sadaharu!
What's up with that guy?
A beef or fish?
Beef and fish.
‐What?
‐Beef and fish, I said!
So, then, Kagura.
I heard that Sadaharu
got kidnapped
by some strange‐looking dude?
That's right.
I don't think I'll be able to enjoy
the trip anymore now.
One more beef and fish!
That's why I told you to leave him
with the miserable hag.
Can I get a strawberry
milk over here?
Man, our trip's trashed
from the get go.
No, what's really trash
is your character.
I mean I couldn't just leave
Sadaharu behind, could I?
Don't you care about
Sadaharu, too, Gintoki?
Kagura, can you just shut up
while we're on the flight?
Man this really sucks.
Maybe we should just go home.
Passengers, please look out
the window on your left.
What you see is the most beautiful
planet in the Solar System,
our mother planet, Earth.
Wow!
It's so pretty!
Yeah.
"Wow", you two?
What happened to "man, this sucks",
you're enjoying this!?
It makes me realize just
how small my problems are.
Yeah, and It really
cleanses your soul.
You don't want
your souls cleansed!
Some stains on your soul are the
only good parts you want to keep!
Good grief.
Don't move.
‐Hijackers!
‐We're being hijacked!
Shut up!
Nobody move!
As of this moment,
our revolutionary forces,
"Burning Fighting Spirit,"
has taken over this ship!
We are going to demand
a ransom for your release
from the government!
How dare you indulge yourselves on
a leisurely trip through space.
The very least you can do
is give up your money
and contribute to
funding our cause!
Anyone who refuses to, or is too
poor to provide us with anything,
‐will be put to death, no questions asked.
‐We've got trouble Gintoki!
‐We do this in the name of the Earth!
‐Hey Gin!
When I die, I think I'd like
a space burial.
I feel like I could
become a star myself.
Yeah, and I'm sure you could!
Hey!
You both really are about
to really turn into stardust!
You there.
What're you doing?
Were you listening at
all to what we said?
Damn you!
You're ten years
too young for that!
Don't you move!
Take that!
‐Amazing!
‐Bravo, Last Samurai!
That was a really stupid move!
Die!
Man, I feel really awful right now.
I should have taken something
for this freaking hangover.
What's this?
Did something happen?
Sadaharu!
You bastard!
What?
Give Sadaharu back to me!
Sadaharu, I'm so glad you're okay!
There, there.
You must've been so scared!
This guy is...
Hey Gin, do you know this guy?
An explosion!
There was explosion in the cockpit!
The pilot and crew are injured!
There's a bomb in the airplane.
It's all over for you guys.
All of you traitors who
welcome the Amanto to Earth
deserve to die.
Attention all passengers!
Is there anyone among you
who knows how to pilot a spaceship?
I don't care who, just save us!
I don't want to die!
What are you doing?
What the hell?
Who are you?
Where do you think
you're taking me?
Listen, if I remember correctly,
you love space ships, right?
You can at least pilot one?
But how do you even
know that about me?
I've seen you before.
You're Kintoki!
Yes, you are.
What are you even doing here?
Long time no see, Kintoki!
What a strange place to meet.
Some sake please!
Someone bring us some sake!
Hey pal, my name is Gintoki!
Get it right!
Gintoki!
If my name were Kintoki then,
we take the title of the show,
wouldn't we!
This is the end of the line.
I am the captain after all,
and I'm going down
with my ship.
The earth it...
it seems so far away.
Did I step on something?
Hey, hurry up!
Those guys are really crazy
to set a bomb on a spaceship.
Gintoki, it's not looking good.
Everyone's starting
to sing Amazing Grace.
Don't worry, Shinpachi.
Just leave it up to this guy.
He's a total airhead, but he
loves ships more than anyone.
He's even traveled
all across the Galaxy.
To someone like
Tatsuma Sakamoto,
moving a spaceship is just like
moving his own arms and legs.
Okay, we are all set now.
Let's do this!
You're right, nothing's in that head.
Hey!
Need me to whack you again?
You see, this is the first time
I've had to pilot a spaceship this big.
I have no idea where to start.
Where's the ship's steering wheel?
Gintoki, is this it?
That certainly is not, Kagura!
Stop abusing the pilot!
I'm so sorry, mister pilot.
Hey, hey, this isn't good.
We're starting to fall towards
that planet down there!
Gintoki, here it is!
It won't budge at all.
Well done, sonny.
Leave the rest to me.
Don't come near me!
I thought you loved spaceships!
But you're totally getting motion sick!
Yeah, I really love spaceships,
but riding in them makes me puke.
What a complicated
love‐hate relationship.
Shinpachi, never mind him,
let me do it!
I wrote an essay about how
my dream is to become a pilot.
You stay out of this, Kagura.
I'll do it.
Because I'm sure it's just
driving a mo‐ped!
No way, you two!
If I put my life in your hands,
I wouldn't have enough lives
‐even with unlimited respawns!
‐Hey, hey...
Amateurs shouldn't be
touching the controls.
I think I know how this
scene's gonna turn out.
The three of you fighting over the
wheel is gonna make it snap off.
I've got to prevent
that from happening!
Whoa!
So this is how it turns out!
It's not funny!
I've made up my mind!
I'm going to go into space.
If I stay here on Earth, crawling
around and fighting the Amanto,
I know how the future's
going to turn out.
Even as we speak...
the Amanto keeps
coming and coming.
We can't fight the tides
of change, can we?
Fighting this war is only sending
our comrades to their deaths.
But I don't want to see any
more of our friends die.
From now on, we've got to look at things
from a different perspective.
A perspective so high,
we can see humans,
Amanto, and the
whole world at once.
That's why I'm going
into outer space.
I'll sail a huge ship through
outer space,
and I'm going to go fly fishing
for all the stars.
How about it, Gintoki?
I think it would be a waste for you
to stay cooped up on this tiny planet.
Come on buddy, what are you
to come with me and...
Hey, heaven!
Send a meteor down on to
this guy's head, huh?
That was really freaky.
The heat is starting to kill me,
now I think!
My whole life was starting
to flash right before my eyes.
Well, at least we managed
to survive the crash.
Survive the crash?
How is this "surviving"
anything, man?
We crashed on a planet whose
entire surface looks like
an old lady's wrinkled butt.
And it's all because you broke
the wheel back there.
Hey I've already forgotten the past.
Men need only look forward
to the future.
Don't play dumb, you hairball!
Oh come on, it's hot enough,
stop getting so heated, guys.
Kagura, are you doing all right?
The sun is strong here.
I'm okay, Shinpachi.
As long as I have my umbrella,
I'll be fine.
But I'm getting really thirsty now,
so I'm gonna go have some
water from that river over there.
River over where?
Wait up!
Don't cross over to the other side!
Shinpachi, it ain't about
how hard you hit.
It's about how hard you can get hit,
and keep moving forward.
That's not how drinking is done!
Gintoki, this is bad!
I think Kagura's about
to cross the River Styx here!
I guess I have no choice.
I'm just a bum.
Hey!
Pull yourself together, Kagura.
All right, Adrian, I'll win the match.
I'll win the match, I'm ready.
This isn't good.
Her eyes are all glassy.
I'll get her some water
from that river over there.
Wait, now you're seeing a river, too?
What are you saying?
You guys can't see it?
Oh, there's even a flower garden!
Oh, it's Oryou.
‐Marry me, girl.
‐Oh, man!
‐Will you marry me?
‐You man are all hopeless!
What's that?
‐It's a ship!
‐They've come to rescue us!
‐We're saved!
Thanks a lot, Mutsu!
So sorry for making you
come out all this way!
And it'll be the last
time I do, Sakamoto.
Our ships are for conducting
merchant business only.
We can't have you, our leader,
always getting into trouble.
And, this had better
be the last time that
you go wandering off
without telling us.
Oh, forgive me.
The girls on Planet Earth
are the best, after all!
Oh, I hope your balls
rot off and you die.
I'm no match for a Tom
like you, Mutsu.
Hey, Sakamoto, what are these?
Ah!
They're the "Kaientai" fleet.
I put it together a while ago.
But although it's a fleet,
they're not for battle.
This fleet is my company
for doing business.
Your company?
Yeah, that's right.
We use these ships to
engage in big business.
We travel to numerous planets,
buying and selling merchandise
across the galaxy.
But recently, space has
gotten pretty sketchy,
so as a self‐protective measure,
we've armed ourselves.
So then, Sakamoto, you're not
just a stupid loser after at all?
Can l go cry now?
It's not military might
nor ideologies
that moves people, it's profit!
Our business bring in profits
for both humans and Amanto.
It helps ease tensions
between the two.
The thing is, I'm trying to protect
our country with my own methods.
Oh, wow!
That's impressive!
Our boss just wanders around
without a goal in mind.
He's a very difficult man
to understand, I know.
But still there's something
very special about him.
Something that attracts everyone.
You too, were drawn to something
he has inside, isn't that right?
I'm really not sure what
it is about him.
But...
What?
What's going on?
I think the heat has
finally gotten to me.
I'm seeing some
very strange things.
Sakamoto!
Don't worry about it.
It's just a hallucination.
...but, I don't think...
Don't worry about it.
It's just a hallucination.
Sakamoto!
What is that thing?
It's a monster!
What in heaven's name is that?
That's a Sand Worm.
It's at the top of the food chain
in this planet's ecosystem.
It's usually docile,
but it must have woken up from
all that commotion we made.
Say what?
Now wait just a minute!
How can you be so calm when
your boss is in mortal danger?
This is what he gets for
always going off on his own.
Hey there, Sand Worm!
Give that mophead
a good beat down!
Especially in between his legs,
if you please!
What's that?
What have you
got against him?
I'm not about to die
in a place like this!
Everybody, get out of here!
Here it comes!
That monster!
It's trying to drag the whole
ship down into the sand!
What?
Use the cannons!
Send it a greeting
with the cannons!
If we do that, Sakamoto,
you'll be killed, too!
Don't you worry about me!
But no, Sakamoto, no!
Ready the cannons!
Hold on!
Do you want to kill
Sakamoto, or what?
He's supposed to be your boss!
Never lose sight of your duty.
We can't endanger the lives
of all of the passengers
just in order to save him.
Right now, my duty is to save
the lives of the passengers.
He always said
"Never lose sight of your duty."
He's a man who left the
war of the Exclusionists
and his comrades behind,
and then he headed into space.
Why was he able to do that?
For the sake of his duty.
He always looked to the future
beyond the battle in front of him.
And he made the tough
decision to labor.
He did it for the good
of his country,
and we gathered together,
drawn by his vision.
That's why, even now, I cannot
flout his principles.
Cannons are primed and ready!
Fire!
Besides, he's not the kind of guy who
would die from something like this.
No, no, no!
I'm telling you, he's gonna die!
No matter how you think
about it, he's going to die!
The Sand Worm is retreating
into the sand!
No! Sakamoto is going to be!
We’ll have to kill it
before it burrows!
Save Sakamoto now!
It's burrowing into the sand...
because you scared it
with all that shooting.
Before you "Do Your Duty",
always remember your manners.
Gintoki!
But where are your
manners then?
Sakamoto!
You spun a very good story
about saving the planet,
but is this where it ends?
Were you just all talk then?
Look at me now!
I'm living my life...
on my own terms!
I see...
I thought if you were with me,
star fishing would be fun.
Sorry about that.
I may not show it all the time,
but I like the Earth.
Go off to space or anywhere
you want, and stir things up.
Fishing for small fries
doesn't suit you.
You're better suited getting
a humongous net
to cast into space and snag
a whole planet.
Well then, what're you
going to do now?
Who me?
Well, let's see...
I think I'll take it easy and
cast my reel right here.
Maybe I'll catch a shooting star
or something like that.
And then, I'll release
it into the sky.
Oh yeah, that is what he told me.
but who knows what really goes on
inside that guy's silver head.
But then...
it's because you stayed
that I was able to go
You stayed down here
on Earth so that...
I could move forward into
outer space without looking back.
Thank you so much.
Gintoki?
As long as you lift me up
every time I sink.
I'll will be able to keep on flying
forever into the skies.
I can fly!
Look! It's Sakamoto!
Sakamoto is alive down there!
That was very reckless.
It looks like he was almost
swallowed up himself.
What was that insane man
thinking doing that?
You said it.
I wonder what those
two are always thinking.
What were they thinking, you ask,
but the truth is they
weren't thinking at all.
I guess...
there's something special
that only they can see.
Good evening! I'm Mopette.
I'm working at a place called
the Girly Boy Club.
Please come visit, everyone!
Wait, why am I doing this?
Hey, Cobra, you too?
The next episode…