I'm sure you already studied
basic factorization in junior high.
Good news: The method remains the same.
Think of the process as splitting an expression
into smaller, more manageable expressions.
No way. Seriously?
Things went pretty well at Capypa Land, so I
invited her to a Hundred Archfiends concert.
Wait, Hiyori!
Hiyori! It's been awhile!
Oh, you've switched uniforms.
Is it that time of year already?
Uh...
It's easy to lose track of that stuff in Takamagahara.
Anyway, I've been really busy
studying invocations with Kazuma.
So I haven't exactly had time to
finish the homework you assigned me.
I'm so sorry! You understand, right?
Maybe I could get an extension?
I, uh...
Wait, that says Yuki... Yukine.
Yep. That is my name.
Yukine!
Whoa, hey!
This smell, this nice smell.
I remember everything!
Yukine, Yato, the promise I made!
I can't believe I almost forgot all of it!
Hey! What's up with you?
Geez! You're an idiot! What were you
thinking? Don't ever do that again, Hiyori!
'Kay. Sorry.
So, anyway. What's Yato been up to these days?
How should I know?
It's been more than a month
now since I heard from the guy.
I wouldn't waste my time worrying. What a big jerk.
Gone a whole month?
My lady hasn't come back yet either.
Hi, Daikoku.
Oh, hey, Hiyori. Long time no see, huh?
She still isn't back? Hasn't it been awhile?
Yeah.
I haven't heard from her since I
was sent home from the latest Colloquy.
It's weird, too.
They usually can't stand the sight of her there.
I don't like this.
I know. Kazuma feels the same way.
He says it's strange there've been all these meetings.
There are so many entries in my date book about them.
And then they just suddenly stopped.
I hope everything... What're you doing?
I'm gonna go out and look for Yato.
Wait, you're gonna do what?
Hold on! Hiyori!
I almost forgot him once before.
But I was so stupid and cocky this time.
Yato!
Idiot! I was so sure I would never forget.
Like I was different or special somehow.
Because our ties hadn't been cut.
But I'm not an exception at all!
It's totally different for unknown gods like Yatty.
Once they've been forgotten, they vanish from existence.
Yato!
I don't even know where to look.
Because, the truth is, I don't know Yato at all.
Stay with me! Stay!
Damn it! What are these creepy things?
They must be Izanami's Beldams. They're under her control.
Don't let them catch you, understand?
You'll be trapped here forever.
Yuki! Hold them off.
Sir.
That was incredible.
The brush really does work.
It allowed me to summon a Phantom using only a name.
That's enough "ooh-ing" and
"ah-ing"! We need to get away from them!
How do we even get outta here?
It's almost labyrinthine, isn't it?
I think it's more than that.
It's like the whole place is expanding.
Why are you running away?
We'll be good friends if you'll stay with me.
Hey! Earlier, when we first tried
to leave, you called her "Mother."
If you're her son, can't you do something?
I wanted to discover more about my own
origins, so I consulted the old literature.
One story says that she abandoned me.
If that's true, then she clearly didn't want me.
So I don't know how our
relationship will make any difference.
It's got me!
They can't be cut!
Just let go, damn it!
Young Master...!
Tatsumi! Utami!
Ooh, I want it!
No, he's mine!
I saw him first!
Come on!
Hiiro. How could you?
He got away, didn't he? You should be thankful.
Now we can fulfill Father's request.
You're the conjurer we were sent to rescue.
I have to get Ebisu out at all costs.
Why do you want him so badly, old man?
What's your game?
Yato god.
I should be all right now. Let's go.
All the previous Ebisus died for this.
I must leave here with the Locution Brush.
Why are you so obsessed with it?
Your other incarnations are dead.
Their work can die with them.
This is what I am meant to do!
It's my purpose.
Is that something you can understand?
The world is filled with senseless
violence and unnecessary pain.
That's why we gods are so important.
But with this Locution Brush,
I'll be able to restrain Phantoms and prevent
at least some of the misfortune they cause.
I can use it to make the world a
better, less painful place to live.
Does that answer your question?
All this, for humanity's sake?
I didn't think guys like that actually existed.
Where are you?
Where did my friends go?
This whole time I assumed he was doing it for power.
Such a fierce will. I'll never have that.
You're a god of calamity. Don't you see?
This is the sort of work you should be doing.
Thank you...
People appreciate this type of job a lot more.
Well done. Very well done, Yato.
Found you!
I've always done everything I was told to do.
It just seemed easier that way.
But that's gonna change.
I wanna be someone people respect.
Someone who she can be proud to have in her life!
Kunimi! Go! Take Ebisu and get outta here!
What? Wait. You can't kill Izanami.
Don't have to kill her.
I just have to hold her off. That much I can do.
Yato-no-Kami.
His name is similar, but he can't be our Yato.
He has a shrine and even appears in stories.
It looks like Ebisu has multiple names.
And Bishamonten also goes by Vaisravana?
Huh. Strange.
I wonder if Yato has another name, too.
There are so many gods described in these books,
but I can't find anything that even mentions him.
There's nothing online, either.
All I can see are his social network pages.
I know! I'll ask Mayu.
The heavens are in disorder?
Yes. I just returned from Lord Ebisu's estate.
They have the whole area cordoned off,
and I was even threatened by armed Sentinels.
Wait, what's a sentinel?
They're the Regalia that serve the heavens.
But Sentinels aren't usually armed.
Something really big must be going on.
We were there recently.
So I know Lord Ebisu has been corrupted.
It's likely he'll perish again.
The heavens have always tolerated his
excessive corruptions and reincarnations.
But not this time. For some reason, this is different.
Yeah, no doubt.
Hm. I was hoping to ask for your help, Tsuyu.
You can find out what's happening in Takamagahara,
and with more certainty than I can.
Will you please consider helping us?
No, Sir Kazuma.
I cannot afford to jeopardize my lord's standing.
We should wait to receive word before doing anything.
Or do you mean to antagonize the heavens?
They have the Gods of Fortune.
They're likely being questioned.
Perhaps even being tortured.
I understand. I know how it is to fear for one's master.
Very well.
What? What's this?
Tsuyu is speaking with the trees.
She isn't a Regalia, you know.
She's the spirit of a plum tree.
It is said that, long ago, she traveled
all the way to Dazaifu to be with Lord Tenjin.
She's been his companion since. For more than 1,000 years.
Her affection for him is deep,
and it will not ever wither.
Conjurer. Masks. Phantoms.
Echoes of discord among the gods.
The heavens are searching for Lord Ebisu and his exemplar.
Really?
There is a peach tree located near the Verge.
It saw Lord Ebisu head into the underworld.
The underworld?
What could possibly send him there?
He had pursuers.
A young male god with a lean frame and
a short girl in white wearing a crown.
That's...
Nora. It must be, right?
That sounds like Yato and Nora.
Oshi!
Just how long you gonna keep
us locked up in this damn place?
We have just discovered that
Lord Ebisu is, indeed, the conjurer.
An edict has been issued for his death.
Punishment for disrupting the heavens.
What?
How are you so sure it's him?
We conducted a search of his residence
and found a large number of masks there.
He also had many Phantoms in his care, evidently.
Furthermore, we discovered that most of
his Regalia are actually Noras. Disgraceful.
But what of Ebisu?
Lord Ebisu appears to have ventured into the underworld.
Likely to procure more Phantoms, we suspect.
That sounds like a bunch of crap. I don't believe it.
It is fact, I assure you.
Lord Ebisu is guilty.
His Regalia confessed everything after being interrogated.
Interrogated? What did you do?
That's none of your concern.
The heavens now intend to call upon the gods.
Lord Ebisu's behavior must be punished.
By death?
Why go straight to capital punishment?
It won't be easy to help him now.
Not with the edict in place. It's over. He'll die.
I'm not givin' in that easily.
Huh?
I won't argue with you about your damn edict.
But if anybody is gonna kill him, it's gonna be me.
Okuninushi?
I'm afraid that won't do.
You will remain here until the situation is resolved.
This way we can assure your innocence.
You must see that cooperation is in your best interest.
Outta my way.
Go on. You heard me, now, move.
I'm bein' nice and respectful to you at the moment.
But remember, I have gone to war with the heavens before.
They called me the Bear!
The Spider! Everyone feared me!
Do something! You have to stop him!
Is this what you want? Another fight?
A god without a Regalia is helpless.
Restraint!
Forgive my tardiness. Are you well, my lady?
Kazuma! I'm glad to see you!
I wouldn't expect reinforcements.
They seem a bit under the weather.
A god without a Regalia is helpless, you say?
That's a dangerous thing to assert.
Really, High Sentinel Oshi.
I may be willing to forget you said it.
Assuming that you withdraw now.
I believe she gets the point, Kazuma.
Benzaiten. Can you handle things here without me?
Go!
While Fukurokuju sacrifices himself to Okuninushi!
We may become the Six Gods of Fortune.
Wait! I didn't agree to this!
We need to get to Ebisu quickly. Choki!
Let's see.
The Underworld Entrance is that way.
It's 20 minutes on foot. You up for a walk?
The entrance to the underworld is a tourist spot.
Pretty crazy, huh?
You're being really quiet. You still upset?
Yato passed through here, I'm sure.
The others said there was no guarantee
it was him, but I think it must have been.
Besides, it's our only lead.
Something's going on with him, and I wanna know what.
I want to hear it from him.
Like I said before, I really
don't think you should come with me.
You can be majorly stubborn sometimes, you know that?
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
You're letting me come?
Yes. But don't do anything dangerous, you got it?
You're really important to Yato.
To both of us, honestly. No matter what.
I swear I'm gonna keep you safe.
Would you like some tea?
Something to eat?
Come. We'll have a nice chat.
We need to split apart and purge the Beldams.
But what about Izanami?
I don't need to kill her. Just
be sure you maintain your blade!
All right. I will.
We need to buy him enough time
to get outta here with that brush!
Young Master, I'm sorry. Are you okay?
I'm fine, I think. But you must be in pain, too, though.
I'm little more than an encumbrance now.
I owe the Yato god a great debt for this.
You'll help me remember that, won't you?
Wha...? What's this smell? Salty, like blood.
No. Not blood. It's the sea!
We're nearly outside. Iwami will be waiting for us.
Oh, dear. It seems all the exits are sealed.
Come, let's return to Lady Izanami now.
I can't fight so many. This is the end.
The new young master certainly loves playing by the water.
What little boy doesn't love fishing?
I only hope he'll live long enough that we
won't need to call him the young master anymore.
Hm?
True.
He reincarnates so frequently compared to other gods.
I wonder why.
What's reincarnate?
To go away and then come back.
I don't understand.
It's what happens when a god dies.
It's okay, don't worry.
You are a very famous god, Lord Ebisu.
A god like you will always be reborn after he dies.
See? There's no reason to be scared.
Young Master.
Borderline!
It won't open.
I don't get it. This should be the entrance. Damn it!
Borderline! Borderline!
Yato...
It's over. I've caught you.
There's no escaping, precious one.
You fool.
Didn't I warn you not to let her catch you?
Now, then. Have a little taste.
This is it. I'm dead.
Lady Izanami!
Please, release him. Take me.
I'll remain here with you instead.
You will? That's wonderful!
Hey, what are you doing? Ebisu!
Yato god. Take the Locution Brush.
I know that I can trust you.
Just make sure Iwami gets this, all right?
Huh?
Kunimi is in dire straits as well.
I'd appreciate it if you'd take him with you.
Wait, what about you?
I imagine I'll die before long.
It's okay. I'll simply be born again, as I always am.
So, please.
I don't accept that.
All of this will be completely pointless if you die!
I wanna help you. Do you understand?
And not because someone told me to!
Why do you wanna die so badly?
I don't actively want to die, but since I
just reincarnate, what does it matter if I do?
What about you as an individual?
Is dying here really what you want?
Is it really what this you wants?
This me? What do you mean?
Isn't there anyone you'll miss?
Someone you wanna see again? Something you wanna do again?
Something I want to do again.
I'm not sure.
I suppose I'd like to eat
another meal at the Olive Tavern.
That'll do.
You have made a wish,and it has been heard loud and clear.
You can pay me five yen later.
Curse you!
We can't escape her. We're trapped.
The exits have all been sealed.
Don't you wanna master controlling Phantoms?
How can you be ready to give up so easily?
If there's no exit, make one.
Drill yourself a hole outta here!
That's completely crazy.
Don't blame me for whatever comes next.
Uki! Tekki! Shuki! Sakki! Gaki! Senki!
Go open a Vent, now!
As you wish!
Damn, he actually opened a Vent. Ha!
I'm burning up. I can't breathe.
Ebisu!
Yato god?
Meow! Meow!
Um, what are you doing, Yukine?
Practicing cat language.
I'm gonna ask Yato if I can have a pet cat someday.
On the next Noragami Aragoto: "Revival."
Meow. Mew-meow!