It was always odd how often he reincarnated,
but this is simply shocking!
To think that Ebisu is the
conjurer that they've been hunting.
I hear that he controls some formidable Phantoms.
And did you know that most of
his Regalia were actually Noras?
A God of Fortune, a Nora-keeping
conjurer? It's practically unthinkable!
I wonder why he would ever do something like this.
That is entirely irrelevant. Taboos are taboos.
The heavens' disorder begets humans'
disorder. Time is of the essence.
Ebisu has been revealed as a Phantom conjurer
and devotee. So, we set forth to slay him.
Quick! Now's your best chance!
Aiha!
Oh, no!
Hey! You okay?
Stay very still, Veena. She'll take your head off.
So I assumed.
Oh, look! This is pretty!
Give him back! Right now!
What excellent luck! It's nearly dinner time.
Come, everyone. We'll have a feast tonight.
Look at this scrumptious dish. Plenty for all, ladies!
Ooh, yes please!
That does look delicious!
Come, come. Eat as much as you'd like.
What are you doing? Stop! Get away from me!
No! Veena!
Get off!
Stop!
Damn it! Can't get out!
Struggling against it will only hurt you more.
I've had enough of this! Lemme go, you old hag!
Kunimi. Are you all right?
I'll live, but just barely.
If it wasn't for the Yato god...
I hope he'll be okay. Lady Bishamon
just went into the underworld to save him.
That's something.
Though I don't think even she is a match for Izanami.
But hold on. Didn't you just say
there was a way we could bring him back?
What were you talking about?
It's a method known as a Soul Call. I don't understand.
You peer into the very depths of the underworld and
call out someone's name to fasten them to the Near Shore.
I believe that's the only way left
to bring him back from Izanami's realm.
So we just gotta call his name?
You really think that will do it?
If it doesn't, nothing will. But it must
come from a Near Shore being with ties to him.
Gods and the deceased are
unable to do it. Only a human can.
You.
To be honest, I've never heard of this
technique being used on a god before.
But we've no other choice. It's worth a try.
Good luck. Be careful.
Yato!
Go on!
Go on! You only have to take one little bite of the
food of the underworld. Then you can stay with me forever!
Won't that be nice? Go on. Have some!
Hold on. Stay strong!
I'm going to try and rip her hair off.
Soon. Almost there.
My lady!
Lady Izanami. I'm sorry to interrupt your banquet, but
it's time for us to leave. The Yato god's coming with me.
Bishamonten!
She disappeared. Wait, could that have been...?
A Soul Call.
It was a Soul Call? So... I can get
outta here if someone calls my name?
Yes, it would seem so.
Yato! Yato!
Milady! Were you harmed in any way?
Wha... What just happened to me down there?
Yato! Yato!
Why? He's not coming.
Hey! Look out!
I don't get it! It worked on Lady Bishamon but
not him? What's wrong? Why can't we Soul Call Yato?
That was a Soul Call?
Well, let's think. Is it
possible that's not his true name?
So he borrowed one? Like in the same way
that my lady goes by Ebisu Kofuku you mean?
That is a possibility.
I do it to obscure my identity as a god of poverty.
So then, who is Yato?
Damn! Using an alternate name?
He's never talked about that!
That's why it didn't work. You must call
his true name to bring him back successfully.
Any idea what it could be?
No.
Kazuma?
I can't think of anything. I'm very sorry.
If we don't do something swiftly,
Yato will be trapped forever.
What is that?
No, it can't be.
The heavens' Punishers!
All they have to do is call my name?
Great! Any minute, we'll be outta here!
Will we?
Do they know your real name? Did you ever tell them?
Yato, my dear!
Aren't you getting hungry yet?
She's right. I never told them anything.
I couldn't bring myself to.
I knew if I told them, they'd hate me.
They'd abandon me for sure.
So I stayed silent. I revealed nothing about my past.
And that means... They don't know my real name.
They can't call me back. I'm trapped.
So it's all over. If the heavens have
chosen to reject me, then I'm finished.
Who are they? The heavens' Punishers?
It looks like they're all gods.
The bastards are hiding their faces.
I guess they don't want anybody knowing the
identity of Lord Ebisu's killers. That's disgusting.
Ebisu! You've already returned from the underworld, I see.
A Vent!
You've opened a Vent into the
underworld? What exactly are you planning?
Look! It's releasing Phantoms!
We must seal it!
No!
We'll never get Yato out!
Wait, everyone!
I implore you to give Ebisu a
chance to explain what he has done.
Bishamonten. Why are you interfering with our task?
Is it not natural for me to stand
in support of a fellow God of Fortune?
I had hoped we might hear Ebisu's reasons
before resorting to senseless murder.
We are standing in front of a Vent that
he opened. We have no need of explanations.
Say what you will, but he has done no wrong!
Bishamon, wait.
I have complete faith in him.
The heavens' decree is not a matter for debate. If
you insist on protecting him, you do so at your own risk.
Conjurer Ebisu! You have violated a
taboo and caused disorder in the heavens.
You are to be cleansed and kept in the Shrine of Passing!
Once, I would have given in. But... I
am no longer so accepting of my own death.
How can you be ready to give up so easily?
Isn't there someone you'll miss? Or
maybe something you wanna do again?
I've finally realized that there are
some things I'm willing to fight for.
My name will endure past my death. For that
reason, I have long taken my lives for granted.
But I'm not ready to give this one up yet.
Fire!
Defend me, Senki!
Yes!
There's the proof! He does employ Phantoms!
You've shown yourself for what you are, conjurer!
Come, Uki! Come, Tekki!
Quickly! Shuki! Sakki! Gaki!
Kinki!
The Vent!
Kofuku!
Kokki!
Let's give this one everything we've got!
Yeah!
Bore!
It's no good. It's still closing! Please!
You need to call Yatty's real name and quickly!
She can't call it if we don't know it!
Yato!
Whoa, hey!
Yato! Please, you have to come back!
Borderline!
Come on! You'll get shot, Hiyori!
Yato! Yato!
Yato! Yato! Yato!
That obviously isn't his name!
It has to be!
Remember? That shrine I made Yato... He was so happy
when he got it. He said it was what he always wanted.
I carved his name on it. How could that name be the wrong
one? He was so happy, he cried. I did carve "Yato," right?
Yaboku!
That light! What's happening?
You... called me.
I did.
It really worked! You're here.
I'm here. Thanks to you.
Alone again. Will no one ever stay with me?
He summoned something from the underworld!
Dispatch it quickly!
Are you okay?
I think so.
You came all this way to look for me?
Ebisu! You're in bad shape. You and the others fall
back. You don't stand a chance against the Punishers.
I can still fight.
Get moving. I'll hold them off.
You shall not escape. Come, Oki!
That's Kiun, Takemikazuchi's Regalia.
Young Master! Kiun is also known as
the Thunder Blade, and for good reason.
Your Phantoms won't be able to stand before him.
What's with them? They're pissed.
I'm sorry for this. Are you okay?
You're still alive!
How did you do that?
Ebisu, just go!
Thanks, my friend.
Running will do no good.
Where'd everyone go?
Into the forest.
All right. Kazuma. Push Kinuha's Borderlines
to maximum power. We're going to take out Kiun.
What? We can't take him out!
Are you certain?
Kazuma?
Yes, I am. Demonstrate your dominance, my Blessed Vessel.
Yes.
You may be a Blessed Vessel, but I
am not threatened by a mere earring.
We really hit him!
Not enough. I need to reach further than that.
I must exceed his Borderlines and strike deeper.
I must believe that I am the dominant Regalia here.
And seize control!
A frightening display. That is what true power looks like.
Bishamonten and her Blessed Vessel.
Is it bad?
Yato!
Yeah, Yukine?
Who the hell is Yaboku?
And since when is "Yato" not your real name, huh?
How could you have lied to us this whole time?
It's complicated.
Can we do this later?
I have to know. Why'd you go into the
underworld without saying a single word to us?
You just disappeared one day and
went and got yourself beaten to death!
With all we've been though, you still
don't trust me. You're an idiot, you know that?
And a terrible master.
Okay, that's enough. Listen to me, I...
No. Let go of me! You'll get blighted, too!
Yato.
Stop...
I know I haven't always been the
best Regalia, but, but I made an oath.
In case you've forgotten, I swore
I would risk my name to protect you!
I haven't forgotten.
You're his Blessed Vessel.
You guys, what's happening?
Is that what I think?
A Pacification Ring!
There you are. The next one won't miss, Ebisu.
How pure is the brightness of thy soul. How
pure the brightness of thy heart. How pure it is.
In the name of Takagi-no-kami,
we wield the heavenly wax-tree bow.
Incredible. I can't believe they're
actually using a Pacification Ring!
I've never heard of that before.
It's something used to quell the
enemies of the heavens. A very ancient art.
One hit from that thing and we're all dead.
I can't believe how far they're willing to take this.
This is insane! There's no reason for
them to drag the mortal world into it.
Sekki!
What are you doing?
You're the one they're going to all this trouble for.
The thing is, you made a wish
and I haven't granted it yet.
Another meal at the Olive Tavern, remember?
You're kidding! But you're not in any condition to be...
I refuse to let them have their way!
I know that I can trust you. Now, let's go!
Should thou be of pure heart, god Ebisu.
Should thou be pure of soul, the arrow shall miss.
Should thou be dark of heart,
the arrow shall tear thee asunder.
Farewell, Ebisu.
Look out! It's coming!
Rend!
He cut through it? Impossible!
That was incredible! Yato god! He truly
is fearless. And so is his Blessed Vessel.
Veena, look!
No! Run, Ebisu!
Today, we'll teach you how to
make fluffy-fluff accessories.
First, get some cotton fabric.
Then you just take it and rip it up.
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"The God of Fortune's Message."
Here. You take it, Yato. You're not gonna wear it?
But it's so stylish! Come on!