It seems that Regalia are
limited in their use of Masked Ones.
They do not have the power to turn Phantoms into puppets.
Only a name-bestowing god is able to do that.
Have you captured a Phantom?
Yes.
Good. Then let's begin at once.
My Earthly name is Ebisu. Bearing a posthumous name,
I don this mask, and proclaim myself a spirit vessel!
Ye names that assemble cannot defy me.
You are bound and beholden to my every order!
Submit yourself to me, and
obey the mask! Yield now, Ryoki!
What're you doin'? Who the hell do you think you are?
The guys who're gonna take you down, that's who!
Ah, kiss my ass!
Like hell I will!
We're gonna kill you!
All right, that's enough!
This is the land of the Rising Sun. Your desecrations
shall not be allowed. Hear me. I am the god, Yato.
I now lay thee waste with the Sekki, and
expel thy vast defilement! I cleanse thee!
Rend!
Uh...?
And thus, it's done, boys. May our fates intertwine.
Make way! Hiyori is coming through! Yeah, that's
right, I'm talkin' to you, shorty! Outta the way!
Look out, there's some gum there, watch your
step. Dandelion fuzz incoming! Quick, cover your ears!
Enough! Can't I walk to school in peace?
Sorry about that, Hiyori. He's
been a little overexcited lately.
'Course I have! See! Get a load of this, yo!
Resident registration card?
That's right! Takamagahara has officially
recognized this lil' beauty as my shrine!
Seriously? They actually approved that thing?
Well, of course they did!
Come on, guys, please! Have a heart!
I visited the office every day right
before closing time until they finally caved!
Man, talk about lax!
I guess government officials are the same everywhere.
Does this new status come with any perks?
It sure does. I can attend things called Colloquies
now. I'm licensed to sell official merchandise.
And I even have my very own holy book and song.
Which you wrote yourself!
It doesn't seem much different than before to me.
Oh, but wait! I saved the best perk for last!
Tad-ah! My own plot of land in Takamagahara!
It's tiny!
You know what this means, don't you?
We'll always have somewhere to sleep.
Yeah, I think I'll stick with Kofuku's place.
And now that we've got a shrine, we can
visit the Heavenly Realm whenever we want to!
Not bad!
That is pretty cool!
And all of it's thanks to you. Really.
I'm glad you didn't give up on me.
Sure. You're welcome.
Hello there! Nice to meet you, I'm
Yato! I just moved into the neighborhood.
I have some young Regalia, and they need their sleep.
I hope you boys don't make too much noise after dark.
Nope! Quiet as mice, don't you worry.
You didn't hear it from me, but apparently...
Oh, my! Positively appalling!
Really!
Guess what, guess what! Yama's got a crush on someone!
Say it a little louder. I don't
think the whole school heard you!
Geez, Ami! Tell me more! What's he like?
I don't really know much about him
except that he's in a higher grade than us.
Oh-ho! An older man, huh? What else? What else?
He transferred here last spring. And his voice!
He sounds just like the Hundred Archfiends' singer!
Hey, Iki!
Hi, Manabu! How've you been doing? Getting
along any better with your classmates these days?
A little bit. At least, I'm not getting bullied
anymore. But still, I'm basically invisible to everybody.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that. School can be rough, huh?
Nah, it's no big deal.
When I do get down though, I remember what you
said: "Find one special person and you're set," right?
Did I say that?
Yeah. You gave me a lot of really good advice.
Use this, sweetie. But remember, if you're gonna
fight rough, then your opponent should be armed, too.
Wha...? I never said anything
like that! No way! You mean Yato.
It was him who gave you advice.
Yato?
Yeah, you know, the guy in the tracksuit. He and Yukine
were in the girls' bathroom, so I beat them up, remember?
No idea. Sorry.
Well, a-anyway. You were really
there for me when I needed it.
And... there's something I've been wanting to
tell you since then. I don't know how to say this.
The thing is, I... I... Like... Like...
I like your shoes! They're really nice! Bye!
Why doesn't he remember Yato?
Excuse me, my lady. You have a visitor.
Yukine?
Hello, Lady Bishamon. I'm sorry to bother you.
What do you want? Are you alone?
Um, yes. I've come to say hello for my loser of a master.
We've just been granted land in Takamagahara, you see.
Here? The Yato god?
Yes...?
A-Actually. That's not all.
I have a personal request. For Kazuma.
Uh...
Could you teach me how to use invocations? Say yes.
I'm Yato's exemplar. I wanna keep getting stronger.
Please help me do that!
Well, I...
Yes. I would be happy to.
All right! I'll work really hard, I swear!
Please don't let them live nearby.
You're awfully quiet. Whatcha lookin' at, Yori?
Yato's been acting really weird lately.
If we're not together, he sends me a
text like every five minutes. Look at this!
Whoa! There're hundreds!
And this isn't even the half of it.
Looks like a good parade. We should go.
They've got a couple's room here. What
do you think, huh? A gondola ride, ooh!
I was just callin' to say hi!
That kind of behavior's only
natural. You are Yatty's first.
That may not be the best way to put it, Kofuku.
There aren't many people out
there who even know Yatty exists.
And nobody was ever so determined to stick with
him before you came along. Honestly, I'm relieved.
This means he can lead another long life.
What?
Yatty has always had a hard time attracting
long-term believers and dedicated Regalia.
He's had to survive within
people's broken, scattered memories.
I can only imagine how difficult that must have been.
Famous gods like me and the Seven Gods of Fortune
are lucky. We don't have to worry about that stuff.
It's totally different for unknown gods like Yatty.
Once they've been forgotten, they vanish from existence.
Like forever?
Yeah. A god is born from the wishes people make, you
know. When those wishes stop coming, he loses his purpose.
He vanishes for good. No reincarnation or anything.
That's why this is so great. 'Cause Yatty has someone
to remember him. A believer he can really count on.
I get his reaction now.
Wait! What if I do forget him? Will he vanish?
No, no. I wouldn't worry about it too much.
After all, he's survived this long, hasn't he?
I'm guessing he's got some other believers out there.
I've always wondered that about Yato. How
could such an unknown god endure for centuries?
He should've vanished long ago.
Bit of a mystery, really.
Now, in order for an invocation to
work, it needs to be tied to a name.
Which leads us to Rule Number
One: Know the name of your target.
But your name's right on your hand where
anyone can see it. Isn't that sorta risky?
Yes. Rule Number Two: Invocations
won't work on those of greater status.
To use an invocation is to impose
submission. It's actually a terrible act.
As such, it could even harm your own master.
So think carefully before using one.
Right.
When you act, do so with confidence. You're a
Blessed Vessel. Make sure your opponent knows that.
What do you mean?
How should I put it? Always treat
your opponent with... contempt, I guess.
Uh...
And Rule Three: There is no such thing as practice.
Restraint!
Too slow! You need to draw more quickly.
Till you're called or it wears off, you're stuck.
Uh... Huh?
Just keeping score. Now, let's go again. Yukine.
Dammit!
Restraint!
Too slow! Again!
Again?
Restraint!
Borderline!
That's hilarious!
Kazuma needs to find a new way of
keeping score. I don't like this one!
Ah! Don't take pictures!
You did your best. That's what matters.
Oh, come on. Don't cry. How
'bout I take you to Capypa Land?
Hell no, you freak!
Aww! But I wanna go to Capypa Land! I wanna! I wanna!
You don't need to drag me along
with you. Just go by yourself!
No way! I can't go on all the rides all alone!
Shut up!
Please!
I wanna see the Capypas! You kown that.
It'll be fun, I swear!
But seriously, I think the three of us should go.
You, me, and Hiyori. We all gotta go to
Capypa Land and get our picture together!
I don't think I've ever seen you look so happy before.
You are unusually chipper.
Well, whaddya expect?
My centuries-long dream has finally come true.
I have a shrine of my own.
I was told I didn't need one. I
almost gave up hope entirely after that.
If only my kid self could see me now. He'd be so happy.
Hold on, you were actually a kid once? I don't buy it!
Aw!
Yato as a kid... Who would have
said something like that to him?
Hey!
Easy, there. He must be real
drunk. He never talks about his past.
All right. I should get going.
Hold on. I'll walk you.
Have a good night, Yori!
I'm happy! So very happy...
Yeah, yeah.
I'm on my own two feet now, and it's all thanks to Hiyori.
On your own two feet? Not if you're relying
on a schoolgirl all the time, you're not.
I've decided. I'm gonna make Hiyori the
happiest girl in the world. You just watch me!
I don't know if you meant that the way it sounded.
It's totally different for unknown gods like Yatty.
Once forgotten, they vanish from existence.
If only my kid self could see me now. He'd be so happy
Yato... I wonder. What kind of life have you lived?
I wasn't sure you would actually come, but you did.
I came because we need to talk, Hiiro.
Do you know how nice it is to hear you say my name?
I've decided I want to end things with you.
And why's that?
Because I've got my own shrine now.
And there's Yukine. He's become a solid Regalia.
I don't want to betray those things.
And that's why you've decided to release me?
Is that so bad?
You have plenty of other
masters. You don't need me anymore.
Tell me, who made me a Nora, Yato?
You're horrible. We've been together all this time.
And now you're just going to
abandon me without a second thought?
Come! Hiki!
A mask!
Not you again...
Come. You should join us.
I think that will do for now.
You know you won't be able to fight off so many Phantoms
without a Regalia. Aw, so weak and sad. Poor little Yato.
You can't exist without a lifeline. Now be a good boy
and do what Father says. Things will be easier that way.
Hey, sorry to bother you. But has Yato come back yet?
Sure hasn't.
He's been gone for an entire week
now. Something must have happened to him!
You know what he's like. There's no way he could
stay silent this long unless there was a reason!
See, that's where you're wrong.
It's not really that unusual.
Yatty goes into hiding sometimes.
His Regalia used to show up here a lot, looking for him.
Still not back? That's my master for ya. Well,
anyway, see ya, I'm gonna go meet up with Kazuma.
Training's a good way to start the morning.
You're working so hard to improve your
skills. In the meantime, what's Yato doing?
How should I know? He's probably with Nora.
He seems upset.
I'm afraid Yato hasn't been by here.
Oh, okay.
Just a moment.
Uh?
It's fine for you to be concerned about Yato, Hiyori.
Understandable, even. But please try to
keep your devotion in check, won't you?
Are you attending school?
You aren't spending more time with gods and
Regalia than with your friends and family, are you?
Uh... No, not at all.
Really? And what about your hobbies? Are
you engaged in ordinary teenage pursuits?
Do you even have a boyfriend, young lady?
Lord, that's quite rude.
Go forth and enjoy your adolescence!
Um, okay.
I can't believe Yato! He hasn't
even told Yukine what he's up to!
Well, he better not blame me if everyone
forgets him! Not that that's likely to...
Manabu forgot. Could that happen to me, too?
No! I won't forget! There's no way!
I hope that doesn't turn out to be a lie.
Whoa! Are you okay?
That's dangerous. Better watch your step.
Hey! Thanks for catching me!
My daughter was murdered. But they won't seek capital
punishment because it was the killer's first crime.
I saw him in the courtroom. He was smiling. Please!
My sweet daughter deserves justice! Will you avenge her?
I've heard that you do that
sort of thing. Say yes! Please!
Keep it. For what I'm asking...
This will be plenty.
So what's the plan? Cut him up on the inside?
Huh?
Come, Hiki.
Who... Who are you? Stop!
I just received a call from the prison
officials. He died from "undetermined causes."
Now my daughter can rest in peace.
Thank you, sir. Thank you so much!
See? People appreciate this type of
job a lot more than cleaning bathrooms.
The Yato god could never perform such
great deeds with Yukine as his Regalia.
You didn't actually think you
could stand on your own two feet?
I don't know what that girl may
have told you, but it was nonsense.
Nothing's changed, can't you see that? It's been
this way forever. Everyone has always abandoned you.
You're a god of calamity. Hiyori and Yukine
will never really accept that aspect of you.
We do. You see, we understand what you
are. We'll never betray you. Or stray from you.
Because we love you, Yato.
Well, what happened this time? I've never
known a god whose health was so fragile.
Easy.
Lord Okuninushi, Lady Bishamoan. We are most honored.
We're the two pillars of the Gods of Fortune, so
it'd be nice if you would quit slackin' off, Ebisu!
A little quieter, please.
Shut up. I'm tired of visiting your sick ass. Get better
and come to my Hawaiian shrine so we can catch some waves.
I'd rather go fishing.
No problem, I've got a boat. We'll
go catch some mahi-mahi or somethin'.
What happened? Were you
blighted? Did you hold an ablution?
I'm tired now.
Pardon me, Lord Okuninushi, Lady Bishamon.
I truly hate to ask this, but perhaps...
Yeah, all right, we get it. We'll
come back later. Don't let him die.
I don't trust those fools any
further than I can throw 'em.
How many more times are his
Regalia gonna pull this kinda crap?
Ebisu does reincarnate with disturbing frequency.
I know! Do those bastards even
care about their master at all?
Why does he bother to keep them around?
Lord Ebisu.
Where have they gone?
Your visitors have left, my lord.
Turn away anybody else who comes by as
well. I need to be alone for a while, thank you.
No one shall disturb you.
What a shame. It seems I'm not very compatible with Ryoki.
All the Phantoms I turn into puppets eventually taint me.
I must rectify that.
Yes, who's there? I asked that I be undisturbed.
Ah, so it's you.
Really?
You've found the Locution Brushes?
Uh! Wait! Stop! I'll turn myself in!
Look at the irises blooming!
It's that time of year already?
Tell me, Hiiro.
Hm?
How much longer are you gonna
make me do this? I've had enough.
How long have I been here? Has it been a month now?
Hiyori! Has it been too long? Has she forgotten me?
What is it?
I need to go back right now.
Back to Hiyori!
Damn it!
Stay back!
Lord Yato. Please try to calm yourself.
Let me out!
Let me go! I want outta here, now!
Stay the hell out of my way!
There you are, Father. Yato's saying that he wants to
leave. I don't understand. He's never said that before.
Really? Are you sure, Father?
Yato. We have a job for you. He says
you're free to do as you wish once it's done.
We need to travel to the underworld
and rescue a conjurer there.
The underworld?
The Hundred Archfiends rock!
No! Zenny's is way cooler!
Tie-breaker. We'll text Hiyori and ask her!
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"The Sound of a Thread Snapping."
Well? She says "victory is decided with fists."
Ugh! Martial arts fans!