Excuse me, Mr. Yato, the light is green.
Will we be there soon?
Hey, it looks like your shoelace is untied.
I've tried very hard, but it's
difficult for me to tie them.
Welcome! Come in, have a seat!
Anything in here sound good to you, Ebisu?
Well, Yato made it back. Finally.
Yeah.
It was nice of Lady Bishamon to give him a
room to recover in. Though I'm kind of surprised.
Yeah.
And Kofuku gave him all those snacks.
He'll be well fed while he heals, at least.
Yeah.
I just hope he'll be okay. You know?
Me, too.
But, I wish I could help somehow.
Huh?
Yukine!
What is it? Is something wrong?
Have you seen Yato recently?
Ebisu came to visit Yato, but now they're gone.
The room is empty, and we have no sign of them.
And, my room had been ransacked.
That was them!
So this is the Olive Tavern?
Feel free to order whatever you want.
I mean it, go nuts. It's Kazuma's treat today.
Well, dear, what can I get for you?
Looks like they have a kids' meal.
How's that sound? Even comes with a toy.
No, thank you.
I'd like a simmered Hamburg steak.
Well, what do ya know?
I had a feeling that's what you'd ask for.
You look just like another
gentleman who gets that all the time!
He must be your daddy! Like father, like son, eh?
Rend!
He cut through it? Impossible!
That was incredible! Yato god!
He truly is fearless. And so is his Blessed Vessel.
Damn monkey suit.
How does Kazuma stand this thing?
Feels like I'm suffocating.
If you don't mind me asking, sir, is
there a particular reason you brought me here?
Because it was Ebisu's wish.
You mean my last self?
Were you friends with my previous incarnation?
Your last self, huh?
Veena, look!
No! Run, Ebisu!
You really did reincarnate.
Yes. From what I've been told, plenty of gods
reincarnate, though none do it as frequently as I do.
The previous Ebisus
I don't care about previous Ebisus.
Far as I'm concerned, there's
only one, and he's gone for good now.
Well, all righty! Here we are!
Good choice! That looks tasty.
Thank you for this food.
It's really yummy!
Oh, yeah? How yummy?
Does it bring back memories?
Hey! I'm talking to you, kid. Well?
Geez.
This really is incredible.
I have never tasted anything so delicious before!
That's not exactly true. From what you had told
me, it sounded like you seriously liked the food here.
Well, this me likes it, too.
Reincarnation doesn't change everything, huh?
You're still as clumsy as ever, that's for sure.
So, kid. You really don't remember anything?
Nothing.
Not the fight we had in the underworld?
Or our mad dash to escape Izanami?
No, but did I really fight you, Mr. Yato?
I guess memories aren't passed down at all, huh?
I don't know.
I was just suddenly here.
From the shrine I could see the beautiful sea and a
quiet, peaceful town full of people who were hard at work.
I fell in love with this incredible world at first sight.
I knew right away that I wanted
to make the people here happy.
A strong desire to make everybody happy.
That must be the natural instinct of the Ebisu god.
What do you mean? Aren't all gods like that?
Wow, good question.
So you're a war god, aren't
you Mr. Yato? What's that like?
I bet you must be a really good fighter.
Yeah, I am. Seems to be all I'm good at.
That's so cool! I'm really
clumsy. I bet I'd be bad at fighting.
Did I at least do okay in the underworld?
Remember? You said that you and I fought one time.
Fighting a war god, I can't believe it!
And what about my Regalia? Was I good friends with them?
Was I the kind of god that made people happy?
I hope so! But maybe I wasn't.
Everyone says the heavens executed me.
So, I guess I must've been a
pretty bad guy if that happened.
That isn't true!
You were a righteous man!
You were willing to sacrifice your life
for the sakes of others! And your strength...
It was unbelievable. I don't even begin to compare to you!
But still, you...
Revert, Kuni!
Ebisu!
Hang in there. Okay?
Come on! Ebisu!
Farewell, Conjurer Ebisu.
Hopefully your new overseer will ensure that
you behave with more discretion in your next life.
May you now decease without worry.
Don't you die! Ya hear?
Don't you dare die on me, Ebisu!
It's all right.
You are very famous, Lord Ebisu.
A god like you will always be reborn.
See? There's no reason to be scared.
Don't worry. It's okay to die.
Ebisu! Come on, stay strong, man!
What about you as an individual.
Is dying here really what you want?
What this you wants?
Ya-Yato god.
I consider myself lucky to have met you.
Ebisu. I'm the lucky one.
No, please! I don't want to die!
But you did. And I couldn't stop it. I'm sorry!
Uh, but, Mr. Yato, what happened wasn't your fault.
Please.
Let me apologize.
As you may know, the heavens issued an official sanction.
Along with my reincarnation,
my exemplar Iwami was expelled.
In exchange, they were willing to
leave the rest of the Mi Clan unpunished.
So I thought about it.
And have I decided to make Kunimi my new overseer.
I don't want anything bad to happen to Iwami.
He's been with me for a long time.
Thanks to all your help, the heavens
haven't been able to find him yet.
I would like to keep it that way, if possible.
In order to do so, I think it would be best for
him to remain here. If that's acceptable to you.
It is.
Thank you so much, Ms. Crazy Chick!
That name. Where did you hear it, Ebisu?
Oh, is it wrong? I learned it from Mr. Yato.
I thought it was weird, but he said it was your real name.
Did he?
You must be curious.
Allow me to recount the facts for you.
The young master entered Izanami's realm in
order to find an underworld Locution Brush.
What does such a thing do?
It gives one the ability to name and employ Phantoms.
Over many incarnations, he
studied methods of controlling them.
He was very thorough and dedicated to his work.
But he was never able to achieve satisfactory results.
So that's why he was gettin' so sick all the time.
And this Locution Brush. Does he have it now?
Actually, it's gone missing.
I am certain he brought it back with him, though.
To be honest, if I had my way, it would stay missing.
I hope he never touches that damn thing again.
Look, what I don't get, is why he was so
obsessed with using Phantoms in the first place.
As you are all aware, the young
master is a god of commerce.
But inevitably, his incarnations realize that
wealth alone is not enough to bring people happiness,
and so he eventually becomes obsessed with
conjurers and the power to control Phantoms.
He convinces himself that he can curb disaster
and use Phantoms for the benefit of humanity.
This is news to us.
All this time, and we had no idea what he was up to.
He only wanted to help people.
Could we have prevented his death?
Things could have turned out
quite differently had we known more.
Yeah, maybe.
I'm sure the desire to help humanity will be
passed on to the newest young master as well.
Yato's at it again, sponging off us
and actin' like he owns the place. Tch.
He just sits around all damn day.
We're not running a charity here.
Would it kill him to wash dishes or fold laundry sometime?
If he did some chores, it might
help him work up an appetite.
We make him all that food and it
just goes to waste while he pines away.
These complaints, coming from you?
The man who swept the attic every day Yatty was
gone so it would be ready for him when he came back?
Admit it, you big softy. You missed him. Right?
I understand. I want him to get better, too.
He'll have help. He's got Yukine and Hiyori.
You're right, he does.
I'm sure the three of them will be fine.
Yukine. Come with me.
I recognize that smell.
Well, out with it. If you've gotta talk, then talk.
Okay then.
From the time I was little, I used
Nora to kill people. So many people.
That's in the past.
No, I kill people. It's what I've
always done whenever I was told to.
Even just recently.
Disgusting, huh? But I really want it to stop.
I don't want that to be me anymore.
You have the determination that marks a good god.
The kind of god that can make people happy.
I keep asking myself: "What can I do?
How can I be like Ebisu?"
Nora.
You're terrible, Yato. Leaving me behind like that.
But I suppose I can forgive you.
You completed your task, after all.
You rescued Ebisu from the
underworld like you were told to.
Tell me something.
Was it a set-up?
Was Ebisu killed in place of my old man?
Are you only now figuring that out?
The heavens were relentlessly
investigating their conjurer.
Someone needed to take the fall.
Ebisu happened to share an interest in
controlling Phantoms, so he was the perfect choice.
All it took was one tiny little nudge from
Father, and the heavens sprang into action.
They got their conjurer, and he got to live.
A happy ending for all!
Now, come. Let's go home, Yato.
Father will be so proud of you.
Like hell he's going with you!
Are you still here? I don't see why.
This doesn't concern weaklings like you.
Say. Do you know the sounds a human body makes as it dies?
Do you know the color blood turns when it dries?
The smell of flesh as it grows colder and harder?
The feel of bones as they're crunched beneath a blade?
Don't you see? You don't have
what it takes to carry Yato's burden.
Y'know something?
This is how you've always been.
You never change.
You always smile just like that.
No matter who weeps or who dies.
But I've changed.
I can't smile with you anymore.
Hiki.
I have a new purpose now.
Thanks for everything, Hiiro.
You can't be serious.
We've always been together. We belong together.
Yaboku!
Not anymore. I am Yato now.
We're done, Hiki. I hereby... release you!
A new purpose? What is it?
Yukine.
I meant it. I wanna change.
I wanna be a different god, one who makes people happy.
But killing is the only thing I'm any good at.
Tell me, what can I do? Be my guide! I need you!
Well, I don't think you need
to do anything different, really.
If all you can do is kill,
slay disaster before it strikes.
I'm here for you. I am your exemplar.
I won't let you become a murderer again.
It's Hiyori.
I wish for Yato to succeed.
May he become what he wants to be.
Yato, you chose Yukine.
And, Yukine, you chose Yato.
So I'm sure my wish will come true.
And if you're not... I have enough faith for all of us!
Yato!
That Storm's huge!
Come, Sekki!
By killing Phantoms, you can save the
people who would become their victims.
And you can keep others from going astray.
I'm certain of it.
So, Yato, your job is to find disaster and slay it!
This is the land of the Rising Sun.
Your desecrations shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god, Yato.
I now lay thee waste with the Sekki,
and expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
I never knew you had such a way with words, kid.
Oh, shut up. Just do your job right, okay?
Sure thing, O' Wise Exemplar!
I don't need your attitude!
I'm back, Father.
So, that weakling actually released you, Mizuchi.
Looks like he's hit his rebellious stage.
Well, isn't that just adorable?
Fujisaki, you ready?
Yeah!
What was so interesting?
Hm?
Nothing, really.