Kazuma. Is there anything to report?
No activity from the heavens.
We should be the first to arrive on the scene.
Aiha, listen. I know we haven't fought together
much lately, but I'll need your strength today.
I hope I'm not asking too much.
No! You can count on me.
Milady.
Pardon me, but if Lord Ebisu really is the
conjurer, as the heavens allege him to be...
It's possible his Masked Ones attacked our clan.
No, I don't think so. It isn't
the sort of thing he would do.
He is unconventional, I'll grant you that. But he
would never disrupt the heavens without good cause.
I have faith in him as a fellow God of
Fortune. I won't let him die needlessly.
Let's keep moving.
Yes, my lady!
A Vent?
A Vent? Now what's going on?
It's been a while, but if I remember
right... Don't Vents open into the underworld?
Let's go get a closer look. This
could be our chance to find a way in.
Yato. Please be all right.
Okay, listen, when we get there...
Where is she?
I... I can't move. I'm being restrained.
Oh, my. What a surprise, meeting you
here. But maybe we've come on similar errands.
Do you have business to settle with Yato as well?
Kugaha! What's he doing here?
You see, I owe him for this.
Do you know how annoying it is to live with only
one hand? The simplest tasks become so difficult.
I mean to change that, and your hand will do nicely.
Yato!
Hiyori!
You stay the hell away from her!
Kugaha! Restraint!
Hm...
It didn't work.
Of course it didn't work.
I am not Kuga anymore.
An invocation requires your target's name.
So it's fairly easy to determine
who has the upper hand here, Yukine.
What do we do now?
You just stay back!
Wait, what?
Hear the shock in her voice? She's
surprised a Blessed Vessel could be so weak.
Say what you want. You're just a
backstabbing Nora. Whose dog are you this time?
Listen to the feisty little boy! You put on a good show,
but I bet you're panicking because you don't know my name.
I've heard it all before.
Gods and other Regalia are constantly insulting us Noras.
But do you even know the real reason why they do it?
Because we Noras are so powerful.
To use an invocation against someone, you must
first know their name. But Noras have multiple names.
You are now experiencing how unsettling, even
terrifying, that fact can be to those who aren't like us.
That's why everyone despises us. Because
they hate uncertainty and fear the unknown.
Because they cannot name you, they despise you?
Don't listen to him. He's messing with your head!
Understand now, Blessed Vessel?
Others like you may enjoy fame and the worship
of many believers, but they amount to nothing.
Not even Kazuma can equal my power. Truth
is, the strong are strong, blessed or not.
Look at little Hiiro. She's a perfect example.
Who is Hiiro?
You know, the one Yato always goes back
to. Little lady Hiiro, dressed in white.
Nora?
You mean you didn't even know her name?
Did your master keep it a secret from you? How sad.
And if he took her with him into the underworld,
he must trust her a lot more than you, huh?
Shut up!
Yukine!
Really? Let's see what you've got!
Nope! Not good enough!
No way! He's overpowering me! But I'm a Blessed Vessel!
Pathetic. Just pathetic.
Hurry! Let's get out of here!
You can't beat a Nora!
Don't let him get to you, okay? You
have to remember! You're a Blessed Vessel.
Yeah, I know that!
You're the one Yato made his exemplar.
I know! I know! But still...
He took her! Why not take me, damn it?
Don't think like that.
Come on, let's play some more! I'm still having fun!
You know how hard I've worked trying
to get stronger. It's all been for him.
I wanted to make sure Nora
never became his exemplar instead.
Now this!
There's no use running away, kids!
He chose Nora.
Look, you should know, Yato told me something once.
And I knew he meant it. Listen.
He told me he'd always wanted to find someone like you.
Thank you, Yukine.
As long as I've lived, you're the first Regalia to
change for me. I'm so gonna brag to everybody about this.
Don't you get it? You're Yato's one special person.
His... one special person?
It's the truth! Yukine...
I found you!
You have to listen to me! Have faith in Yato!
Borderline!
Wow! Amazing! You did it. You beat him!
Let's go, Hiyori. Let's find Yato.
Damn it.
Hold on! Stay strong, Yato.
I did it. I actually did it! I managed to save Ebisu!
And I didn't do it for my old
man. I did it because I wanted to.
Don't you dare die, Ebisu! If you give
up now, I'll kick the crap outta you.
Hear me? That's a promise!
Is this right?
Do all of these names belong to me? So many.
If you include the local and historical variants.
I'm almost like a Nora then.
And it looks like the name Ebisu has many
different meanings. Including "drowned corpse."
With all these possibilities, who am I, really?
One story claims that you are Master Hiruko,
the first child of Lord Izanagi and Lady Izanami.
Hiruko.
Yes, that's right.
Though, I now call you Lord Ebisu because it is
the name you are most widely known by these days.
I see.
I wonder why my parents didn't want me.
Ebisu. Ebisu!
Come to your senses!
He's awake!
Are you all right?
Bishamon.
Thank goodness. With the way you were
lying there, I thought you had been executed!
Can you stand, Lord Ebisu?
Lady Bishamon! Kazuma!
You two! Why are you here? I told you to stay away!
Who is that man?
Lord Ebisu.
Be careful! You're still weak.
The Yato god. He didn't make it out.
He's still in the underworld.
The Yato god is still in the underworld.
You must hurry.
I don't understand. What would he be doing there?
He came to the underworld for me. To bring me back.
I-If we don't help him, he'll be Izanami's forever.
Hold on! Why would Yato go save you?
None of this makes any sense.
Bishamon, please help him. For...
Did he die?
He's passed out, that's all.
Over there!
I've got you! I've got you! Now, come to me,
my dear. My beautiful, wonderful, darling, Yato!
No!
Where are you?
Will you be all right? Here, hold on.
Let me wrap this up for you. There, all better.
You'll be fine now. Right?
Yeah, sure.
I don't know how you're so calm.
We're gonna die down here if we don't
find a Vent. You realize that, don't you?
Yes. But as long as I'm with you, I don't mind.
Hiiro's always been different from other people. It's
like she's totally fearless. Nothing seems to faze her.
And as a Regalia, she's never once tainted me.
Maybe...
Maybe I could stay with her.
Hiki.
What are you planning to do?
I'm gonna find a Vent, if it kills me.
I will get back to them, whatever it takes!
Even though you might already be long forgotten?
I have to get out of here.
And cut ties with the old man.
I have to get back to them!
Yato!
Found you!
You're mine now!
Yato!
Come to me, my darling. Come.
Please, Lady Bishamon!
How can we get into the underworld?
The entrance is sealed. Now so's the Vent.
It doesn't matter. You can't go.
It's Kofuku and Daikoku.
I'm glad you're here.
That's right! Help us! You can open up a Vent.
You absolutely cannot go into the underworld.
It's no place for humans. You'll never leave alive.
Lady Bishamon, I beg you.
Please take me into the underworld!
Do what?
You must let me do this. I have to save him.
I'm prepared to risk my name for my master.
Yukki.
Hm?
If you're that determined, there's only one option.
You must enter the underworld as someone else's Regalia.
Are you willing to become a Nora?
He can't do that!
There is no need for you to sully
your name, Blessed Vessel of Yato.
You can leave this to me. I'll bring back your master.
Are you sure?
Kura.
Stay and look after Ebisu.
Yes, my lady.
It makes no difference where he
hides. The heavens will find him.
Hopefully, he will recover enough
to explain what he's been up to.
We must clear him of these charges.
Now, let's hurry. Choki!
Right!
Bisha, please save him.
Please get our Yatty back.
I will.
Kokki.
Don't do anything reckless.
We want all of you back here in one piece!
O band of fiends treading upon sacred
land! With the Kokki, I pierce you. Bore!
Let's go!
Right!
Lady Kofuku, stand back where it's safer.
Those fools! I'm surprised they even survived down here.
Something just flew up my skirt. Ew!
Stop it! We need to stay calm.
Why do you suppose Yato entered the underworld?
Ebisu claims Yato went there to save him. I
don't know what his true goal might have been.
But there's one thing I'm certain of.
The Yato god has people waiting for
him. So we must make sure he returns.
Scouting the area. Follow this
waterway. There's a cave at the end of it.
And Yato? Can you determine his location?
Look at the ground, my lady.
Hm?
Do you see a thread-like substance?
It stretches down toward the cave.
It's not thread, it's hair!
I think we can assume it belongs to her.
Whoa. What happened? I did try to hold back a little,
but even so, no Vent of mine should close up so quickly.
That last Vent seemed to close out
of nowhere, too. What's going on here?
Is she sealing up the underworld?
Are you ready to give up and stay
here with me? My sweet. My Yato.
Huh?
You're Izanami, the queen of the underworld?
Who are you?
One of the Seven Gods of Fortune.
Bishamonten. I seek the Yato god.
Will you turn him over?
If not, we fight. No holding back!
Yeah, you know who you're up against?
A war god with a Blessed Vessel!
Bishamon? You came?
She's caught him.
There's no way he'll be able to escape on his own.
Listen, everyone. Don't even
think about trying to defeat her.
If we're not careful, we'll be stuck here forever.
The underworld is Izanami's realm.
We're here for the Yato god.
When we have him, we leave at once.
Right!
How dare you! I was having a
lovely tea party with my friend.
You interrupted us!
Impressive. It's no wonder
she's known as the supreme war god.
Still...
Nothing happened? But how is that possible?
A blow that strong and it did nothing?
We're in big trouble!
Everyone focus! We all need to work together now!
Right!
Fools! You shouldn't have come.
Hurry! Get outta here! If you're
looking for Ebisu, he left. I helped him.
He should be safe.
Be quiet! You suicidal maniac!
Don't you want to be rescued?
Rescued? What are you...?
Yato god. I have hated you to the core of my being. I
loathed you, and I loathed myself for being saved by you.
But whatever I've said before, you weren't
to blame for the deaths of the Ma and Ha clans.
I have actually known that all along.
Their deaths were my fault.
Yato god! I hated you because it
was all I could do to keep going!
In spite of that, you've saved me twice.
Are you telling me you came all this way
to say "thank you"? You're freakin' crazy!
You can say whatever you want about me, but
I always pay my debts. That is why I am here!
You famous gods are only so brave
and daring because you can reincarnate!
Do not think me so complacent! I don't
wish to die. I'll fight to remain who I am!
Veena.
Yato god, hear me well! Your friends
await you outside. Yukine and Hiyori Iki.
That's right! So don't you give up!
They're waiting...
Hiyori and Yukine. They're waiting for me!
My lady, let's try again.
Bore!
It's no use! The Vent is just closing right back up.
Damn it! They won't have a way out!
Please, Milady.
Yato.
Bore!
A Blessed Vessel and a human girl.
I see. They are his purpose.
They are why he keeps fighting.
He's awoken!
Ebi! Are you okay?
You can help Yato. If you wish to bring
him back from the underworld, there's a way.
However, not just anyone will do. It requires a human.
Hm.
What's wrong, Kazuma?
I can't decide if your bath should be 105 or 106 degrees.
On the next Noragami Aragoto: "Your Voice Calls Out."
What do you think?
Honestly? I don't much care either way.