Ready. Go!
Ready... Go!
No use. It won't work.
Easy. Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm just a little tired.
Her Cord is starting to fade.
Being here in her ethereal form is dangerous.
If we don't lift the Scourge
soon, her physical body will die.
This is my fault.
I played right into Kugaha's hands.
Before long, he'll have won.
Please, Veena.
Tch! Nice try! Sekki!
Now!
Confine!
You're finished.
Come, Saiki!
No.
Yukine!
Hard to believe he sacrificed himself to protect you.
Maybe now you understand the agony of losing a Regalia.
I'll put you out of your misery.
Yukine! Yukine!
His name. It's still there!
Sekki!
That light. What is this?
Impossible...
This is what happened with Kazuma.
He wasn't much as a new Regalia. Just a small nail.
But rarely, very rarely, a Regalia will transform.
It happens only with the most sincere
and loyal of them. The Blessed Vessels!
Wow. That was pretty amazing. Are you okay?
I'm not sure how, but I think I am.
Everything happened so fast. I guess I got carried away.
Before I knew it, I'd turned into two blades.
Thank you, Yukine.
Huh?
As long as I've lived, you're
the first Regalia to change for me.
I'm so gonna brag to everybody about this.
Brag? You mean, about me?
A god of calamity with a Blessed Vessel?
Her sword didn't break me!
Yeah! You're awesome, kid!
What do you say? You ready to get Hiyori back?
Let's do it!
My lady!
Heh. I didn't expect that brat to
evolve at the last second. This is perfect.
Stop! You let go of me!
That medicine should be wearing off.
What's happened to her? Don't tell me
I can't believe it. Our lady's been corrupted!
No, this can't be happening!
Tch! Not again!
I don't think so! You're staying right where you are.
No, stay back!
I don't want you blighted, too!
Are you really surprised you've been tainted?
You did arm a Regalia. And kidnap an innocent!
Let's end this! Give Hiyori back now!
We would never do the things you're suggesting!
Then how do you explain the blight?
She got like this because one of you tainted her.
Badly.
Yes. He's right. But who is it?
Time for another round of the blame game.
I think you know how it's played.
Kinki!
Milady, I'll take you away from here!
Attack him.
Huh?
If we want to save everyone, we have to kill Yato!
That's one crazy chick.
Have you seen the shape Bishamon's in?
It's only a matter of time
now until Yato finishes her off.
And while he's at it, maybe he can get
rid of her whole entourage for me, too.
What an idiot Kazuma is.
Honestly, he's as blind as they get.
He couldn't see that something had to be done.
Fortunately, I was willing to step in.
Soon, Bishamon will be reincarnated,
and then I'll be the exemplar.
Why? Why would you do this to her?
It's simple.
Our master's a failure.
Her time is up.
Like an idiot, she insists on
helping every pathetic spirit.
And then pats herself on the
back for being so kind and motherly.
My Lady!
She's ended up with a pile of junk Regalia,
all pretending to be one big, happy family.
That's the mighty Bishamon?
She's not my master, I'll tell you that.
Now, stop crying.
There's no need for you to suffer on
behalf of a wretch like her. I told you.
Be patient until after the reincarnation.
The next Bishamon won't scorn you like this one has.
And as the new exemplar, I'll have
the power to absolve you of guilt.
Hey! No! Wait!
I'm not gonna let you hurt Yato!
That's my boy!
Milady! Your blight is worsening!
I'm begging you, please stop!
Where is Kazuma?
He's the one we really need right now.
Aki! Okinu! Take everyone inside.
We can't lose ourselves in this chaos.
Have anyone who can do so draw a borderline.
Right! Yes, sir!
Come on, everybody! This way!
There has to be something else I can do.
How do I make sure we all live through this?
Someone help.
I'm burning up.
Please. Please, my lady!
We can't endure this pain. Just release us.
Please do it. Release me!
Even corrupted, you can still fight?
You may be crazy, but you're damn tough.
Come, Jinki!
Okinu!
You're beyond saving now.
Run!
Everyone into the hall! Hurry!
Oh, it's you, Doctor!
Don't look like that. It's your lucky day.
You second-string Regalia are finally going to be useful.
Doctor. Why?
Now we're almost there.
Damn it!
Aiha?
Please. Please forgive me.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
I'm the one who tainted our master!
You have to stop Dr. Kuga!
If you don't, everyone's going to die.
What? Everybody?
Kazuma!
What she says is true. Our master has been corrupted!
No one knows what to do.
All hell broke loose after Yato showed up.
If we don't act quickly, I don't know what could happen.
I'm coming, Veena. Aiha, we'll talk later.
All right, let's go.
Please, get on.
Me, too! You said Yato's here.
You need to return to your body at once!
The Scourge is gone, but you're
still in critical condition.
Please, Kazuma. Do this for me. Take me with you!
No! You're being foolish. I will not let you die this way!
Now, return immediately!
No! You have to take me!
I'm the one who can stop Yato.
I knew it. He's doing this to force a reincarnation.
So it would seem.
Apparently, he used some sort of medicine to
conceal the blight until the opportune moment.
I apologize. You were right to be suspicious.
What a fool I was.
I blindly trusted him because he was our master's curer.
I was an idiot not to see through his ruse.
Choosing trust is usually the best course.
We Regalia cannot afford to mistrust one another.
Such discord is toxic to our master.
In extreme cases, it can even be fatal.
No matter what, we must continue to smile.
For our Lady's sake.
That's what I've always taught our family.
Always. But now we have disgraced her.
Once again.
Umm. Are you sure that really helps?
Seems like it must be tough.
It sounds like Bishamon handles
things a lot differently than Yato.
He has no trouble complaining whenever he's in pain.
And Yukine's not usually shy
about sharing his feelings, either.
That can lead to a whole lot of
bickering, but I like that about them.
It's sweet. You can tell they're
actually close to each other.
More family than friends.
But Bishamon and her Regalia are
quietly suffering to keep up appearances.
Isn't that sort of hard on everyone?
A Phantom!
What's it doing here?
Masked Ones are a far cry from ordinary Phantoms.
Your Borderlines won't last a second against one.
A hearty appetite!
I wonder how much agony Bishamon
is in after losing so many Regalia.
More to go! So many more!
Find the rest of the survivors, my Phantom friend.
Hunt them down and kill them all!
It's headed this way.
We should get out of here.
What are you waiting for? We need to go now!
Why bother?
Huh?
More names have disappeared.
My Regalia are dying.
This can't be happening. Not again.
My lady! Help!
Please, my lady!
They're dying again!
He's taking them from me again.
Damn you!
She's using her Regalia even after being corrupted?
What the hell is she thinking?
You're better off just cutting it down.
Yato?
Once a bond has come unraveled, there's no mending it.
Careful not to become entangled,
or it will choke you as a Scourge.
Yato, look out!
You're better off just cutting it down.
Yato!
Hey. I know that voice.
Yato! Stop fighting her!
Veena! It's worse than I thought.
It's really her. Hiyori's
okay! Look, Yato, do you see her?
Hiyori's here! She's fine!
Bishamon's not who you want!
You were tricked. She's not the one who kidnapped me!
It was our curer.
Kugaha wanted you to kill Veena.
If you did, she would reincarnate. That's what he's after.
So you can stop fighting now, okay?
I'm sorry, Veena! I should have realized it sooner.
Veena!
Sorry, Hiyori. The fight's not over.
Give them back. Give me my children back!
So I'm still the bad guy here, is that it?
I get it. That's what kept you going all this time.
That unjustified hatred.
Whatever. That's fine.
I'm just a filthy Nora-keeper.
So let me do what I do best.
Your Regalia clearly need killing. I'll do the honors.
Yato!
What do we do? We can't just stand here.
Kazuma!
Now, then.
If you'll excuse me, I have another appointment.
Your dear master is about to die.
And that is something I would like to see.
Milady!
Yato!
No, stay back!
Pretty soon, she's gonna take us down with her.
We have to kill her.
Don't worry.
She'll be reborn, and you won't really
be the one doing the killing, anyway.
This one's all on me.
It's okay, kid. Killing a god's no big deal.
Veena. Listen to me.
There's something... I've never told you.
The Ma Clan's death wasn't Yato's fault.
It was mine.
I asked him to do it.
I betrayed them. They died and I survived.
I wanted so badly to tell you the truth.
I can't protect you, master.
I'm just a little nail.
Please, you must find other Regalia to serve you.
Better ones.
No. I never wanna go through that again.
I don't need any other Regalia!
All I need is you!
In the end, I wasn't able to say it.
Nor could I stop you from hating Yato.
You needed that hatred.
It's what gave you new strength.
So you see, I'm a coward!
I only wanted to be with you.
Your words that day were bitter, but
they filled me with joy. I reveled in it.
And now, I've made you weep yet again.
Blessed Vessel? That isn't a title I deserve.
I've failed you in every way.
Just look at us now.
This is where my guidance has led us.
I've put you through such anguish.
I don't deserve your forgiveness, but I am sorry.
Oh, Milady.
So much pain.
She must have been holding this in for
years, for centuries. She's sobbing like a child.
It's done, Bishamon. Time to end this.
You have to let your Regalia go.
Yugi.
Kinu. Tsugu. Kazu. Karu. Kura.
Kazuma. I'm sorry. So sorry.
It's happened again.
How many members of my family are dead?
I don't know if I can bear this!
I don't get it.
Yato hasn't killed anybody tonight.
So who did kill them?
The mastermind of this little scheme.
I can't believe you're a Blessed Vessel
now! Let's have a party to celebrate.
We'll dress all in white, buy a huge
cake, and throw rice at each other!
Uh, no. You're thinking of a wedding!
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"What Must be Done."
I'm not marrying you, dude!