The entrance to the underworld.
And it's open, so he must already be inside.
Hey.
Are you sure we'll be able to get back out once we go in?
Entering the underworld is like jumping into a vent.
It's basically asking to get eaten by Phantoms.
Phantoms are the least of our worries.
Or have you forgotten? This is where Izanami dwells.
She's very different from other gods, right?
Deathless as she is.
The eternal queen of the underworld.
As long as life and death exist, she lives.
If she catches you, there's no escape.
You'll be stuck in the underworld for eternity.
Frightening, isn't it? But don't worry.
You've got me by your side. I'll protect you.
And if I rescue this conjurer, you'll
give me my freedom, as promised, right?
Hiki.
I can act as a protective barrier as well.
Don't tell me that precious
Blessed Vessel of yours can do this.
Let's go.
Hey there, ladies! Have I got a sweet deal for you!
I'll pass.
Hear me out, okay?
My uncle gave me a bunch of free tickets to Capypa Land,
and I was thinking it would be the
perfect chance to hang out with you-know-who.
Who are you talking about?
Oh! You mean that guy you like.
Who else?
The joys of adolescence.
So, I need you guys to come, too.
What do ya say?
You want us with you on your date?
Actually, it's gonna be more of a triple date.
A triple date?
Yeah, he's bringing some friends with him.
So that's where you two come in. Pretty please?
Mm...
What is it about Capypa Land?
Aw! But I wanna go! I wanna go to Capypa Land!
I wanna! I wanna! I wanna! I wanna!
I couldn't say anything then,
but I actually wanna go, too.
Are you in, Hiyori?
Uh... I don't think I can.
I made plans to go with someone else.
With who?
Uh, with...
Great, then it's decided!
We're going next Sunday.
Huh?
Okay, fine. Count me in.
Youthful escapades, here we come!
But I don't wanna go on a date with
someone I've never even met before.
Don't worry! We'll be there, too.
It'll be fine.
Hey, Hiyori! Have you seen Yato late...
What is it, my lord?
Just let her go. She'll be much better off this way.
Well. I should be leaving for the Colloquy.
I'll see you when I return.
I dunno if I'm up for a date this weekend.
Wasting my time with another damn Colloquy!
Didn't we just have one?
I'm a busy god, ya know?
I gotta take my wittle Inaba for a wabbit walk!
Nushi! I missed you so much!
It's Lady Ebisu Kofuku!
The infamous god of poverty?
He's done for.
Kofuku!
Her enthusiasm can get the best of her.
As her exemplar, you should train her better!
And what the hell're you thinking,
using our names without permission, huh?
Ebisu and I'll sue the pants off you, just wait!
Aw, now I wanna kiss you even more!
Such a big, burly god.
And he's afraid of little Lady Kofuku.
Poor Okuninushi's always been like that.
Very superstitious.
Hi, Bisha. Hi, Kazu. How're you doin'?
We're fine. But I'm surprised.
It's rare to see you here.
Yeah, it is. Hey, have you seen Yatty by any chance?
Yato?
That's right.
Since he's become a resident of Takamagahara,
he should've received today's summons.
Exactly. That's what we were hoping for, anyway.
Has something happened?
Seem's Yatty's done a disappearing act.
He's been in the Lower Realm for a whole month now.
A month? But what about Yukine?
It's strange. Yatty was so happy
he'd finally become an official god.
He was even excited about the Colloquies.
That's why we're here. Maybe he came, too, you know?
Careful not to make eye contact. They'll spot you.
Yeah, I know.
Do you see that water? Bathe in it.
Gross!
Endure the stench. It'll keep the
nasty Phantoms from picking up your scent.
This brings back memories, doesn't it?
Of all the time we spent together.
All the things we did. We were unstoppable.
Together, there was nothing we feared.
Well, you remember.
How many days have passed on the outside?
I've heard time flows differently
here, just like in Takamagahara.
Could they have forgotten me already?
Yato.
A mask. Is the conjurer here?
Ebisu?
I've gathered you all here with good reason.
There has been an important
development regarding the conjurer.
Have you learned the conjurer's identity?
Who is it?
To change a Phantom into a
puppet, it must be granted a name.
Giving names to those?
What a terrible thought!
It would mean instant corruption!
Quiet, all of you!
As you've said, this conjurer must endure a great deal.
Which indicates a god, a highly revered one, at that.
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
The Seven Gods of Fortune?
No! You're wrong. It isn't us!
What's more, how could you expose us like this?
Anonymity is guaranteed at a Colloquy!
Uh-huh!
Fear not.
I am not implying that any of you is the
conjurer, but why are there only six of you here?
We've received a written tip, in fact.
It reads as follows:
"I have witnessed someone
naming Phantoms in the Lower Realm.
The granter's name is Ebisu."
Liar!
Whoever wrote that phony tip is full of it!
Therefore.
Ebisu and Iwami, his overseer, are under arrest.
Ridiculous! He's on his deathbed!
Leave him alone. He would never...
His residence is to be cordoned off and searched at once.
Furthermore, all his Regalia are to be interrogated.
Unbelievable!
Given this matter's sensitivity, we kindly ask
that the rest of the Gods of Fortune remain here.
That will be all.
What are you doing here, Yato god?
Just what I was wondering.
What brings you to the underworld?
Is that Yukine you wield?
No. This is Hiiro.
What a relief.
I was hoping we'd catch up to you.
Now we can fulfill Father's request.
You're the conjurer we were sent to rescue.
Hold on. The old man's connected to Ebisu?
What old man? I'm lost.
I'm afraid I don't know what
the two of you are talking about.
Is this "old man" you speak of your father, Yato god?
Hm. Your refusal to answer only makes me more curious.
And when I'm curious about something,
I can be very difficult to deter.
Regrettably, I don't have time to spend on this now.
Ah. I know.
We can talk further on the outside.
When would be a good time for you?
You're missing the point.
I came down here to rescue you.
You came all this way to rescue me?
Well that's very kind of you.
All right. I've had about enough of this cesspool.
Let's get outta here.
Hey, where the hell are you going?
I can't leave just yet.
The Phantoms have increased in number.
Don't make eye contact!
Oh, look at that.
There appears to be one heading right for you.
Hiki!
Oh, here's another one.
Stop looking at them, will you?
Hey! There's one behind you!
My, that was excellent work.
I can see that you'll come in very handy down here.
I'm terribly uncoordinated, you see.
In fact, I can't even tie my own shoes.
Tell me, are you any good with a bow knot?
Well. I'm better with bondage knots.
Oh? That's very impressive.
Are you for real?
I'm entirely reliant upon my Regalia.
How rude. I should have introduced them by now.
Please forgive me. Kuni. Tatsu. Uta.
You brought your Regalia with you?
I'm Kunimi.
I'm Tatsumi.
I'm Utami.
Incidentally, Kunimi ties the
best bow knot you'll ever see.
Next time, let's give these "bondage knots" a try.
Of course, Young Master.
What's with you people?
It seems the path splits here.
This guy's gonna make my head explode.
Young Master!
What is it? What's wrong?
Whoa, hold on! Are you blighted?
It's nothing to worry about.
Guessing it was your conjured Phantoms that did this.
Unfortunately, my invocations are still far from perfect.
For now, I merely control
Phantoms using masks I've collected.
This system does have its merits, however.
It may sound odd, but there is a certain satisfaction
in naming and employing a Phantom as one would a Regalia.
Although, I must admit that it has been far from easy.
I am tainted by each failure, you see.
Masked Ones demand even greater strength.
They're far beyond me at present.
Not for much longer, though.
Soon I will have the necessary power.
You're in bad shape.
We need to get you out of here soon.
No, thank you.
These Phantoms are nothing. Not compared to what's ahead.
You don't wanna go any further, trust me.
Why, because of Izanami?
She's the reason I'm here.
I came to see Izanami and get a Locution Brush.
Now if you don't mind, let's be on our way.
Where are we?
I haven't had guests in ages!
Wha...? Hiyori?
Well? Come in, come in!
No! It can't be her.
The woman from the Olive Tavern?
Make yourselves comfortable!
What, are you blind?
That is clearly a high school girl!
High school girl? You're crazy.
Hey, I see the way you're looking at her, you old pervert!
The woman from the Olive Tavern is
definitely not a high school girl.
No mere teenager can make steaks as good as hers are.
What the hell are you talking about?
Would you care for some refreshments?
Don't eat or drink anything here.
If you do, you'll never leave.
Please have some. There's plenty.
Oh, what's wrong? Do you not like me?
Don't be shy now, of course you do!
You're not alone. Everybody likes me.
Can I tell you a secret, though?
I think I like you best of all. Let me show you.
Get away from her!
Ah, I understand now.
She must alter her appearance
based upon the person looking at her.
She dons the guise of someone close to
you to make it easier to trap you down here.
The queen of the underworld. Izanami.
You should know I have no intention
of negotiating fairly with her.
That would be a waste of my time.
Huh?
Um, hi. I'm Akira Yamashita.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Aimi Tabata.
And I'm Hiyori Iki.
I'm Seki.
My name's Abe.
This girly version of you is so cute!
So... who is he? Which one of them's your guy?
He isn't here yet.
Sorry I'm so late.
Hi. I'm Fujisaki.
Don't worry about being late.
I'm just glad you could make it.
Really, thanks for coming! This'll be so fun!
Where would you like to go first?
I hate waiting in line.
Let's get some Fast Tickets.
Whoa, what's that you've got?
Limited edition Hundred Archfiends swag!
You've heard of the Hundred Archfiends?
Uh, yeah! Hasn't everybody? Hun... dred...
Arch
fiends!
Uh... So much for cute and girly!
Any idea what they're talking about?
It's this obscure band nobody's ever heard of.
Plenty of people know who they are!
I'm sorry.
You kinda got dragged along today.
Oh, no. I'm sorry!
I guess Yama can be kinda flaky sometimes.
It's okay.
She mentioned you would be coming, too, so...
Well, where should we start?
I'm a little lost. I've never been here before.
Heh.
Lady Izanami. I was told that I
could find a Locution Brush here.
One that is able to control Phantoms.
I have come to humbly request that you give it to me.
How rude.
I'm sure you meant to say that you came to see me.
You are the second one to come asking for a brush, though.
Huh?
These are the objects in question.
No way...
Enki.
We would like some tea please, Enki.
Right away.
I created these myself.
I made them because I wanted friends.
Friends who wouldn't leave me. You see...
Everyone who looks upon my true form leaves.
Always.
You want this badly, don't you?
If I give it to you, will you be my friend?
Your friend?
Unfortunately, being your friend
is not something that I can do.
However...
Yato. Don't fight her. I mean it.
She's on an entirely different level than us.
Not even I am sharp enough to harm her.
My offer is a simple one.
I will give you the Locution Brush.
In exchange, one of you will stay here and be my friend.
That part is up to you.
You should think hard before deciding.
The agreement will be binding.
I'm sorry it worked out this way.
Wait, what are you saying?
You're the one who will remain here in the underworld.
I came for the brush. I mean to leave with it.
I came to save your ass, and
this is how you say "thank you"?
Awesome!
I always wanted to get my photo taken with one of those.
I know, me, too!
I wanted to get one with me and, uh, me and...
Restraint!
Borderline!
Excellent!
It's just you!
Hello! Thirsty?
Quit ambushing me like that, will you?
It's my version of a pop quiz.
So the Colloquy's over, then?
No, they sent all the attendants
home early for some reason.
That almost never happens.
Huh. What about Yato? Was he there?
No.
Okay.
So, Yukine. I heard Yato's disappeared.
Is that really true?
Yeah. Apparently, it happens all the time.
He seems a lot calmer than I would expect him to be.
I know all too well how a
troubled Regalia can harm its master.
He's staying calm for Yato's sake.
You've made great progress.
Huh?
Okay, then. Today, we'll practice Restraints.
Great! I'm ready!
Kunimi is a rare type of Regalia
that can control its master's movements.
Unarmed combat is his specialty.
Tatsumi and Utami are very capable, too.
I may not be a god of war, but I am a god of fortune.
And as such, I have great confidence in my luck.
Oh.
I hear you reincarnate all the time.
Sounds real lucky.
My Masked Ones come at a prince.
They've devoured many of my previous incarnations.
Tch. You talk about reincarnating like it's nothing.
Why are so bent on being a conjurer?
Let me ask you.
Why do you exist, Yato god? Why are you still here?
I did some research before I came to visit you.
I like to be informed.
Formally, you're considered a god of war,
but some stories say you're a god of calamity.
Those instances aside, I've only
heard your name in a few oral traditions.
If you're so close to vanishing already, then why...?
Stop talking!
I was born from people's wishes, just like you!
So I don't wanna disappear.
Tell me what's wrong with that, huh?
I wanted to make them happy, that's all. Okay?
You're not lookin' so good.
That blight must be pretty painful.
I envy you.
Huh?
The way you care about your life.
It's not something I've experienced. Such passion.
You have the determination that marks a good god.
The kind of god that can make people happy.
Hurry! You can't take much more.
It's a mistake to underestimate my men.
Come, Hi...
Come, Toki!
That was such an exciting fight.
And it looks like you get to stay and be my friend, Yato!
I have what I came for. Shall we go now, Yato god?
Bastard! You planned this all along?
I did tell you I had no intention of negotiating fairly.
And you, Hiiro!
What gives?
You didn't tell me you served Ebisu, too.
Sorry.
Small world, isn't it?
Kunimi says I named her five incarnations back.
Is that right, Tsutsumi?
Yes. It's been awhile.
This is sort of an awkward reunion, isn't it?
I mean, I know you're a Nora
and all, but this is a lot to take.
It's strange, but I suddenly feel much closer to you.
Stop! Ew!
You're leaving? You can't do that. You
were supposed to stay and be my friend!
We need to hurry.
Hiki!
What are you doing? Come on!
I'm glad I was able to see you. Goodbye, Mother.
Hold on. Mother?
Please don't leave me! I'm so lonely.
So very lonely. I won't let you.
You'll stay here with my other friends!
I suspect it would be best if we
got out of here as quickly as we can.
Uh-huh.
Hiyori and Yukine are out there waiting for me.
I will make it back to them.
It's so strange.
I feel like I'm close to remembering
something, but I don't know what it is.
Oh! A Capypa with a crown.
They'll love this little guy!
Of course, they won't share, so I'll get two.
Or maybe one for all three of us!
Three for you, too? They for your family?
No. Actually, they're for...
They're for... Who?
What's going on? Something feels wrong.
The parade's starting in a second.
We should get going.
What is it?
I feel like I'm forgetting something.
Something that's really important.
Ready? We...
So many glittering, colorful lights.
Fireworks flooding the sky.
A sparkling parade procession illuminating the night.
Even the people's smiles seem to shine
brightly, giving off a rosy, cheerful glow.
But to me...
To me it all seems distant and dull.
The light feels so far away.
It seems like someone's missing.
Someone who should be next to me, smiling.
Who did I wanna get a picture with?
Who did I want to give a present to? Who isn't here?
Or am I wrong? Am I imagining things?
You okay?
Why? Why can't I remember?
I wanted to come here with him. To get a picture together.
I... I wanted to stay by his side, but now...
Oh, dear. I forgot my hand cream.
Hand cream? That's very dainty of you.
It's very difficult to count
money with dry fingertips, you know.
On the next Noragami Aragoto: "A Certain Desire."
Yeah, of course I know!
I know all about money!