Welcome home!
You made it! Oh, I'm so happy!
I thought you were goners for sure!
And the rest? Lady Bishamon and the others?
They're safe, too. They got some things out in the open.
Hopefully, that means she'll stop hounding me.
None of this has been easy.
But, personally, I couldn't be
happier. No more crazy war god on my tail!
And even better than that... I've
finally got myself a Blessed Vessel.
Wha?
Really?
Seriously?
No way!
For that wretch?
No one has ever deserved it less!
That kid's too good for you, Yato.
A Blessed Vessel?
It's something pretty rare. Yukki
risked his name to protect his master.
Just like what Kazu did for
Bisha. They're very special Regalia.
So, you've finally found the one
for you. That must make you happy.
Kinda.
All right! We're celebratin'
tonight! Let's go prep for a party!
Woo-hoo!
That reminds me... Uh-oh! Oh,
no! My advancement exam is today!
I'm sorry! I really have to go!
If you'd wait a moment please, Hiyori.
Yes, what is it?
Well, Yato?
About our agreement. I trust you remember.
Please, Tenjin. Just take us up there.
This is for Hiyori.
I'll agree to help you on two conditions.
First, no one is to know I was involved in any way.
As for the second...
I assume you know.
Now that you've returned safely, you are
to sever your ties with her once and for all.
No...
You actually agreed to that?
It's become painfully obvious that Yato's
involved you too much with the Far Shore.
That entanglement has repeatedly
placed you in unnecessary danger.
Lord Tenjin, I don't think...
You are not yet one of the dead.
You must send her back where she belongs
now, Yato. It is the right thing to do.
You know it is.
Sekki.
You're going to cut our ties? Are you sure, Yato?
I'll forget you, though. It'll be like we
never even met. And you're okay with that?
Well, I'm not. Don't do it. You
can't! It's not fair! Please! Yato!
I'm not ready to lose you yet!
I gotta say. These uniforms are a
whole lot cuter than our old ones were.
Yeah! I wasn't sure I liked them that much
at first, but I think they're growing on me.
You know, Hiyori, for a little while there
it looked like you weren't even gonna graduate.
You only barely woke up in time to take the exam.
What about you? You were wide
awake, and you still almost failed.
Yeah, I don't wanna talk about it, thanks.
Heh.
So, what club are you gonna join?
I still haven't decided.
Tennis or basketball... Or a Culture Club, maybe.
What do you think?
Hm. I'm not really sure.
What'll she join? The Yato Club, of course!
What's up, Hiyori?
Join now and guess what? You can
get your very own fluffy-fluff scarf!
Hey, where's the fire?
Maybe she's joining the Track Club.
Yato Club! Yato Club! Yato Club, Yo!
There it is!
Her first Insta-Snooze in this grade!
Yo! Where you goin'? The Yato Club is looking for you!
Will you please stop following me?
Come on, you idiot! What are we doing?
Yato Club! Yato Club! Yato Club!
Leave me alone!
Listen to her!
If I had to guess, I'd say...
they haven't severed their ties.
Yato's hopeless. Honestly, Mayu,
I don't know why I even bother.
What does he intend to do now?
My lord.
Huh?
It's time. We must be on our way soon.
Lady Bishamon.
God of war though you may be,
your recent actions are unacceptable.
This isn't the Month of Gods! To
have a Colloquy now? It's unheard of!
Your corruption and its aftermath have caused
a tumult. You have shaken the very heavens.
How do you explain your behavior?
The Yato god's attack was
unexpected. I admit, I responded poorly.
Do you mean the snake god? Yato-no-kami?
Certainly not! I've no part in this.
A charlatan must be using my name!
Indeed, you're right. It was not you I meant.
I speak of a nameless god without a shrine.
Oh, yes. There are some like that. Wretches
who seek to benefit from others' status.
True. As a matter of fact, I believe a
god of poverty is using Lord Ebisu's name.
What I would like to know is how a shrine-less
one was able to ascend here in the first place.
Never mind this nameless god. He's of
no concern. The Masked Ones are, however.
Masked Ones... Phantoms employed using Scourges.
Never before has one appeared here in Takamagahara.
What of this Kugaha who brought
them? Why did you decide to release him?
Indeed.
From him, we could have learned about
the conjurer who created the Masked Ones.
Perhaps I acted hastily.
However, you may be interested to know that I have
since learned he was not bound by the name "Kuga."
I presume he was the conjurer's Nora.
A Nora, you say?
You believe someone here granted
him a name. Is that your accusation?
Nothing like that! It isn't my
intention to accuse anyone of anything.
What troubles me is this conjurer's
ingenuity and ability to deceive the gods!
This incident has unsettled both Heaven
and Earth. There will be consequences.
Phantom numbers will increase.
You are to carefully observe every Phantom's behavior. I
expect timely reports regarding any Masked Ones you find.
I will issue a search notice for this Kugaha.
The Colloquy is adjourned.
So, she really was corrupted?
And he's still her exemplar? Even after failing her twice?
I'm finished. Finally.
You must be exhausted.
I admit, it is fatiguing.
I know I am at fault for what happened. But
as a god, I cannot afford to bow down to others.
I understand their displeasure, though.
There's no trace of Kugaha. No one knows
where he is. If he truly is a Nora, as we suspect,
he may already have returned to another master.
Most likely the one who created the masks.
Naming and employing Phantoms...
Who would do such a thing?
It's essentially like asking to
be corrupted. That's inconceivable.
Truly.
How could such a god continue to exist?
Unless... the one responsible is
already something that shouldn't exist.
Bishamon!
Hm?
Good to see ya! How's it goin'?
Okuninushi! Everyone!
Oh! All Seven Gods of Fortune!
Those grouchy bastards.
Glad that's over. Thought those geezers would
never leave you alone! My ears need a break after that.
Yours, too, Inaba?
Everyone can hear you.
Let 'em listen! Anyway, forget all that.
Since we've got the whole gang together again, I'm
throwin' a party at my shrine in Hawaii! Wanna come?
Where's Ebisu?
He was just here a second ago. Anybody know where he went?
Ah, go figure. I don't know what
that guy's up to half the time, anyway.
Well, drop by if you can. You know where
we'll be. It's gonna be awesome! Aloha!
A party. Will you go?
No. I'll pass.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Ebisu, of the Seven Gods of Fortune. I'm here
today because I have heard some stories about you.
I have a proposition to make.
Iwami.
Sir.
I would like to purchase your Blessed Vessel.
Is it insufficient?
I can bring you another briefcase, master.
Boss!
Wake up, Yato god. I want Yukine.
I am willing to pay any price.
Uh... Any price at all?
You're not really gonna sell
me! Even you wouldn't do that!
Yukine. If you do join me,
I'll pay you one million a month.
Ow.
I know that sting! You're feeling greedy,
aren't ya? Don't you try to hide it from me!
Maybe it was just a static shock.
You are behaving distastefully, Sir Yukine.
You should not be so easily swayed by money.
It's unbecoming of an exemplar.
An exemplar? Who? Wait, me?
That's correct.
You are Lord Yato's unique, irreplaceable Regalia.
And that makes you the same as an
exemplar. An exemplar leads the way.
He serves his god as a guide of virtue.
In short, he is a half-god.
Lose your way, and your master will
surely perish. You must be steadfast.
Indeed. Your position is vital.
It is you who protects Lord Yato's name.
Perhaps you could see about acquiring
the services of a different exemplar.
Or perhaps we could share Yukine.
I would welcome his talent, even as a Nora.
Uh...
It's rather sad. A god residing in another's abode.
And surely a Blessed Vessel deserves better than that.
Have you no shrine of your own, Yato god?
Enough! I'm not joining the Yato Club!
Um, where did all of that come from?
Oh, you mean the money?
Don't tell me...?
What do you take me for? That stone-faced
creep, Ebisu, randomly showed up here.
He wanted to buy Yukine from me. Told me to
take the money and build a shrine. Real nice guy.
How could you do that to him?
I didn't sell Yukine! Have some faith in me, will ya?
I don't need somebody else's help to build my shrine.
But, you know, it's possible Yukine
will decide he'd rather go with Ebisu.
It's a confusing time. Kid's all mixed up inside.
So, I learned something from Lord Ebisu today.
Yeah? What was it?
Apparently... I'm Yato's exemplar. Crazy, huh?
Not that crazy. I'm one, too.
What? You are?
Uh-huh.
But I thought exemplars were like, you know, leaders
and stuff. Really respectable, upstanding Regalia...
Unlike me?
It's true that an exemplar sets the standard
for righteousness when there are lots of Regalia.
but I'm Kofuku's only one.
Just like you're Yato's only Regalia.
Right. His only one.
And remember, Kofuku's a god of poverty
who spreads disaster. She isn't helpless.
She doesn't need much protecting, so she says. My lady
is always telling me I shouldn't risk my name for her.
All I need to do is raise her when she
reincarnates. That's my duty as her exemplar.
It's how I protect her. Now, Lord Ebisu relies on his
exemplar, Iwami, to see that his wishes are passed on.
His reincarnations and Regalia
changes tend to be pretty intense.
And then there's Kazuma. You know
how devoted he is to Lady Bishamon.
Exemplars all have their own way of protecting
their masters. And none of them are wrong.
Question is, how do you want to protect Yato?
So, um. What are you gonna do with the money?
I'm gonna give it all back! What else would I do?
Hello and thank you for calling! Fast, affordable,
and reliable. Delivery God Yato at your service!
So, how can I help you?
S-Sorry, I, um...
Uh...
Hey, um. I'm pretty sure this is a job offer,
but it sounds kinda dirty, if you know what I mean.
You can't afford to be picky about work! You slacker!
Oh please, God! Don't hurt us!
Please, God. Please, God. Please, God.
What the...?
The client's grandmother was
the victim of a bank transfer scam.
Wouldn't she be better off just going to the police?
She doesn't wanna make a big deal of it, apparently.
Hey. Five yen isn't a lot of money. You
ever think about raising your rate a little bit?
What, and stop getting clients altogether?
Forget that! I'm trying to get my name out there.
I want people who believe in me. Not money.
A little money wouldn't hurt, though.
You, too? Typical! My Regalia are
always quitting because of money.
I don't get it. Humans seem to
be incurably fixated on the stuff.
Why should you be any different?
Go join Ebisu for all I care!
Oh! Now I see! With Regalia always leaving, you
don't have much choice. You have to turn to Nora.
Makes perfect sense. That's
why you haven't gotten rid of her.
You need her as your fallback. That's kinda sad, actually.
Here we go. That's the post office box the
old woman sent the money to. He's our man.
Sekki.
Sekki!
Man, old people are such suckers!
Uh. I'm not seeing a Phantom, here.
Yep! There it is. The size of a flea!
We'll cut only the Phantom.
No good. It's too small for me to cut.
In that case...
Wait!
Geezer. More. More.
What was that?
I think that Phantom's got a thing for money.
Money, huh?
Yato! You've gotta revert me! Hurry!
Huh?
Just do it! And you keep chasing the Phantom.
Back already? Is Yatty with you?
Hey, what are you doing up here?
Acting like an exemplar should.
Huh?
I can't let myself become fixated on money.
I need to remember I've got a job
to do. I can't put my desires first.
Wait, I'm coming, too!
So easy!
Want more. Not enough.
Want a lot more.
Look! Money! It's raining money!
What the hell are you doing with my money?
He's got a plan, right?
Money! My sweet money!
I don't know much about it yet, but I'd guess
an exemplar isn't supposed to give into greed.
How do you want to protect Yato?
Who will be your exemplar? If
the choice is between me, and her...
... then it should be me.
Wow, kid, you've really changed.
Woo-hoo! Money-money-money! Gimme more!
More! More! More!
More!
That's a big one!
All right! The Phantom took the bait. Let's go!
Dude! You're still stuffing your pockets?
"Who needs money?" You act all high and mighty,
but you were gonna sell me! C'mon, admit it, you were!
I'd never sell you, I swear! I do want money, though!
So the truth comes out, huh?
I need money for a shrine!
Why are you so obsessed with having a shrine?
As your exemplar, I feel I should make a suggestion.
Throw the money away, Yato.
Sekki! Let's go!
Yeah!
Want more!
Ha!
More money! Want more money!
This is the land of the Rising Sun. Your desecrations
shall not be allowed. Hear me. I am the god, Yato.
I now lay thee waste with the Sekki, and
expel thy vast defilement! I cleanse thee!
Rend!
More money!
A bank transfer scam? How awful! Be careful,
Hiyori. You never know who you can trust these days.
Yeah.
Money is nice, but as they say, it can't buy happiness.
Ah. I need to go take a look in my brother's room.
Well done! I hear you turned
down Ebi's offer. I'm proud of you.
This kid's really startin' to grow up on us.
Way to go, Yukine!
So... where's Yato?
He really wanted a shrine. He's pretty bummed
out about it. This is some hardcore pouting.
You know he's really upset when he refuses to eat.
Yato, is a shrine really that important?
Yeah, it is. If you don't have one, it's
like no one cares about you or anything you do.
All right, then.
Here. This is for you.
Whoa.
A mini shrine?
You made it, Yori?
That's right!
I used my brother's materials. I actually had a
lot of fun doing it. I was up working all night.
Wow!
Hey, this is awesome! You finally got yourself a shrine.
I hope it'll cheer you up.
He-He's crying?
Why are you so obsessed with having a shrine?
It's my dream, okay?
I've always wanted one. Ever since I was
little. But no one would ever build one for me.
Humans may not think much about it, but
being given a shrine is a very big honor for us.
Because there're people who believe
in us. People who appreciate us.
For a god, not much matters more than that.
Hey, man, watch the snot! Tissues! We need tissues!
Aw, geez! You're gonna get snot all over your new shrine!
So, the Yato god can't be persuaded
to let go of his Blessed Vessel. Hmph.
Ebisu! Join me for a drink tonight!
Very well. What time would
you like to meet for this drink?
You know, whenever.
On the next Noragami Aragoto: "God of Calamity." And how
big is this drink? If there are two of us, it must be...
I don't think you get the concept.