Ah!
Stop.
Stop. Please don't kill them.
My lady! Help!
Please, my lady!
Lady Bishamoan!
No!
Yato.
Hello there, and thank you for calling!
Fast and affordable, Delivery God Yato at your service!
Damn. It keeps slipping.
Yes, of course! I'd be more than happy to accept the job!
I can't do these handwritten fliers, Yato...
Right!
Put down the pen. We've got work!
There!
Hiyori! Breakfast is ready!
I'm coming!
Good morning, Mom. Good morning, Dad. Did you sleep well?
Not too bad.
Yes, thank you, dear. Now, come eat.
I opened that jam we got as a year-end gift.
Oh, yummy!
I hear that you did well on your practice exam.
The actual exam is what matters, though.
You wouldn't wanna be held back a grade!
See you later!
There's no need to run!
Hello there, Hiyori!
Oh, good morning, Miss Sasaki.
Have a good day!
Morning! Staying warm?
I'm trying, Ami. Hey, where's Yama?
She headed in early, the poor thing.
Sounds like she bombed the practice exam.
Oh, really?
Hey, Yama!
Yori! Perfect timing!
Why's that?
Do you know the answer to this one?
Oh, this is a hard one.
Let's see. If I remember right...
Thank you. With your help, maybe I'll actually pass.
You can teach me everything I need to know.
My secret weapon!
Be careful, though. Trying to learn too
much, too quickly, can backfire on you.
Yeah, you're right.
With my luck I'd cram all night only to
fall asleep during the exam the next day!
Uh, Hiyori?
Huh?
Ah-ha! Hiyori's patented Insta-Snooze trick!
Man, I really hope she doesn't do this during the test.
Rise and shine, Hiyori!
Great. Looks like my soul slipped out again.
Oh, well. What do you say we go for a walk?
Smells nice. Is that...?
Have you prepared yourself? Because the time has come.
Here we go! Almost there! And...
Clean baby!
Oh, wow. You mean you actually know how to change diapers?
That was nothing compared to changing a cloth diaper.
Are you that surprised, though? I've
been around for a long time, you know.
Who'd let you near their baby?
Hey guys! Can I come in?
Hiyori!
I'm not interrupting, am I?
You sure slip out of your body a lot.
How'd you know where to find us?
You doing some Delivery God work?
Yeah. Yato the babysitter god, at your service.
I guess his parents are sleep
deprived because he cries all the time.
Really? He's not crying now. He seems perfectly happy.
For the moment, sure.
Where's his mom, anyway?
Snoring it up in the other room.
Can't blame her. She hasn't gotten any sleep in a week.
Hey, he's laughing!
He's looking your direction. I guess he can see you.
Actually, it's pretty normal for animals and young
children to perceive those of us from the Far Shore.
His skin's so soft.
He likes you. I think he's asking you to pick him up.
Huh?
Uh... Oh! He's heavy! And why's he squirming? It's freaky!
Here. Put your left hand on his back.
Support his head and neck with your whole
arm, and put your right hand underneath.
O-O-Okay. Like this?
What did I do wrong? Why is he crying?
We have company!
A Phantom?
Let's go! Jungle Savate!
Nice one! Hiyori, keep an eye on the kid for me.
Huh?
Come, Sekki!
Ready, Yukine?
What? No!
You're sharper than I realized!
Wait a second! The room's too cramped.
Don't forget, there's a baby in here!
I commend you for being concerned.
We must take care not to cause
undue harm to those of this world.
You'll need to hold back.
Great. How do I do that?
Let's review, shall we?
You draw a Borderline.
A line between what gets killed and what survives.
What, or who, I kill is up to you. Understand?
Yeah, I think so.
This Phantom is acting really weird!
It's... healing itself?
The kid's doing it.
But how?
The mirror. This Phantom is just an image.
One created by the kid himself. See what he's doing?
He probably wanted somebody to play with.
So he kept reaching out to his
own reflection in the mirror.
The longing and vulnerability that
poured out of him summoned a Phantom.
Unless we do something to stop it, it will
eventually possess his mother, stealing her humanity.
That's awful!
I have to say, this thought energy
seems unusually strong for a baby.
Okay, then. What do we do?
We slay the real one... The one in the mirror.
Keep the baby there, Hiyori.
He needs to see his reflection.
'Kay. Got it.
This is the land of the Rising Sun.
Your desecrations shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god, Yato.
I now lay thee waste with the
Sekki, and expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
That was incredible, Yukine!
That's my Regalia for ya!
See, I knew you could do it.
He should be safe now.
Well, that's a relief.
But... What do we do about all this?
We scram, obviously.
Huh?!
That's horrible Yato!
I can't believe you!
Especially when you're supposed to
be setting a good example for Yukine.
A mask?
You called for me, Lady Bishamoan?
Yes I did, Kazuma. Please, come in.
How may I help?
How much time do we have remaining until our next patrol?
It's today. We have it planned for the Fiendish Hour.
I see. It's almost time then.
Is something troubling you?
Well, as a matter of fact, I
had an old nightmare this morning.
Clashing with Yato again after
all these years may be to blame.
I'm sorry to hear it. Are you all right?
Yes, I'm quite fine.
However, I'll need you to locate him again for me.
I must know if we've overlooked anything.
Right. Shall I inform the curer, to be safe?
Yes.
What? No way!
It's true.
But... I'm sure you cleaned up in the end though, right?
Of course! I insisted. We couldn't leave it like that!
You can guess who she made do all the cleaning!
Must've been terrible.
Show some respect for the working class!
You can start by feeding me.
I think I'll have grilled eel today.
You don't place orders.
You'll take whatever I give you, and you'll like it!
Ah! I think you punctured a lung!
Here, Yukine. You'll need to do this over.
And check your work using a dictionary this time, okay?
Uh... Okay.
You're such a strict teacher!
Really? Am I?
How's he doing, anyway? Does Yukine have some book smarts?
It kinda varies. He's better at some subjects than others.
Overall, I'd say he's an eighth grader.
Wait! Eighth grade is only one below me!
Oh, jeez. What about that time...?
It's been a while since I slept with someone...
Uh-oh! Maybe he thought I meant slept, slept with someone!
What? Is something the matter?
Oh, no. Nothing! Everything's fine.
It's just dandy. Nothing's wrong at all!
Heh. You try to act mature, but
you're still young in so many ways.
Good thing I'm here. Somebody has to look out for you two.
You should be thankful.
I may not be a big deal now, but just you wait!
Before much longer, the whole world will know my name!
Yeah! I'll have my own shrine and everything!
Yeah, I dunno. You've been saying
that for over a century now, Yatty.
You're skeptical. I get that.
But it's different this time. 'Cause now, I have this!
I give. What's it do?
A miraculous lucky cat made of magic gemstone!
Its beckoning power is guaranteed
to draw people to the bearer.
It was given to me by one Master Ishizaki,
a fortuneteller who once appeared on TV.
The bottom says it's "made of plastic."
Huh?
And it's not beckoning.
Look at the paws. It's doing a "hurrah" pose.
What?
Talk about a gullible consumer.
How much did that fortuneteller charge you?
Two hundred thousand.
Wha...?!
How could you blow that much money?
That kind of cash...
Wait! Please! I bought it for us!
If my luck improves, so does yours!
Poor Yukki. It must be rough being Yatty's Regalia.
Yup.
My spleen! You got my spleen...
Aren't you supposed to be putting
your money towards a shrine, Yato?
Anyone need the Delivery God?
God-like powers, at your service!
Ah, jeeze.
Any job... mildew scrubbing,
diaper changing, even Phantom slaying.
Any job at all, just five yen!
Yato. Look.
Huh?
There's a Storm brewing.
Hey! What was that for?
Hey, that's Bishamon. Right?
Whew. That was a close one.
We would be in for a world of hurt if she saw us.
Let's just go this way.
So, I've kinda been wondering.
How long do we have to keep avoiding her?
Huh?
I mean, I owe Kazuma for helping me with the ablution.
I'd like to talk to him and,
you know, maybe say thank you.
Yukine.
You will stay away from Bishamon.
Help me! Someone please help!
A spirit! It's being eaten by Phantoms.
Kuraha. Let's go!
Please wait a moment.
What is it now?
You mean to save another spirit?
Of course I do.
We failed to save her life before.
If I fail her again, what kind of god am I?
Best to target the wings.
Gaiki!
Fire!
Jinki!
Atop northwest building. Distance: 31!
Suki!
Do it now!
Saiki!
This is the land of the Rising Sun.
Your desecrations shall not be allowed.
Hear me, I am the god, Bishamon.
I now lay thee waste with the
Saiki, and expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Ruin!
Revert, Yugi.
She and Kazuma are such a perfect team!
Another stellar performance from the mightiest war god.
Shuki.
This will hurt a bit.
Okay, let's make this quick.
Adhesion between the left biceps,
brachii, and both shoulder blades.
Try to avoid tendon damage.
Endure.
There is only one way to remove
phantom blight from a spirit.
And that's to cut it out.
There. That should be all of it.
Spirit, you are lost and adrift.
You have nowhere to go and nowhere to return to.
Thus, I grant you a place to belong.
My name is Bishamon.
Bearing two names, you shall remain here.
With these names, I make thee my servant.
With these names, I use my life to make
thee a Regalia, fit to be wielded by a god.
Thou art Mine!
As Regalia, Ryoki! Come, Ryoki!
I don't understand. Why is she a broken mirror?
Once it has been torn, the unfortunate
spirit cannot become a proper Regalia.
Oh.
That's part of the reason she
goes out of her way to save them.
Wow. She's such a kind god.
Look out, my lady!
Whenever you're ready.
I'm so sick of Yato's crap.
Always giving orders without bothering
to listen to me or ask how I feel. Ugh.
No way! Are you serious?
Yeah!
Come by my place if you don't believe me.
Okay, I will!
I'm telling you, man, this game is killer.
Hey.
Hey. Don't ignore me, kid.
Huh?
Find some place else to sit. You're smashing the flowers.
Huh? U-Uh? Hold on a second. Are you talking to me?
Who else would I be talking to?
But, that means you can see me, though.
How is that even possible?
You're a Regalia, like me, aren't you?
Oh.
Small world, huh?
Revert, Mine.
W-Where are we?
You're in Takamagahara.
This is Lady Bishamon's manor.
And as of today, this is where you live, as well.
Huh?
You are part of the family now. Welcome home.
From this day forward, Mineha, you're one of us.
I expect everyone to treat her warmly.
Yes, Lady Bishamon!
Perhaps we ought to have somebody give
you a little tour of the manor. Anybody?
Sure! I'll do it.
Tsuguha.
I'm still new enough that getting the
chance to explore the manor is fun for me.
I see. Well, thank you.
Let's go!
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
This is all part of being a master.
Regalia are former humans.
Although their flesh is gone, their spirits remain.
Fear, suspicion, envy, resentment.
They feel all these things.
And the pain of a Regalia with a
clouded mind is also borne by its master.
You mean you've been stung?
I believe I told you not to worry about me, didn't I?
Let me worry a little, at least.
You have so many Regalia... maybe it's time to slow down.
With each new weapon you take on,
you endanger your health that much more.
Anyway, moving on.
What news is there on Yato?
Uh.
Have you found him?
No, not yet.
He's a god of calamity.
I can't let him live.
Yuck.
It's very bitter. You should take it more slowly.
Enter.
Yes, Kugaha?
I've readied your ritual bath, my lady.
I appreciate it.
If you will excuse me, then.
You're looking quite pale today.
Shall I prepare a medicinal bath?
Please.
Lady Bishamon.
What is it?
I've heard a rumor that I find rather troubling.
Some time back, Kazuma left the manor following a
meeting without informing anyone he was doing so.
Perhaps you recall the occasion?
Yes. I do remember that happening.
The rumor I spoke of concerns where he went that day.
An ablution ritual.
That was apparently held by the calamity god, Yato.
Absurd.
Yes, of course it is. What a ridiculous idea.
Uh-huh. Yeah, sure. Okay!
I'll let him know for you. Hey, Yatty!
That was Yukki calling.
He says he'll be back a little late.
Huh?
That darn kid is always goin' off some place.
And it's not very long before dark, either.
Yato.
Could you do me a favor and give
this homework to Yukine for me?
I've labeled a few assignments he still needs to do.
Sure, but does that mean you're leaving?
Yes. I need to get home.
I've still got some prep to do for tomorrow.
So, uh, Hiyori.
Have you seen those new
Four-Cheese Melty Buns by any chance?
They sure look tasty, don't they?
Huh?
Mm-mm!
They're the kind of thing you have
to try before they're gone forever.
You know what I'm talking about!
Yeah. I'll look into it for you.
Cheese bun, score!
You haven't forgotten what you're
supposed to be doing for me, have you?
Huh?
I hired you to fix that little issue I'm having.
You know, how my soul slips out of my body!
You said you'd take care of it, remember?
You even took my five-yen coin!
Oh, yeah. I'm on it! Totally! No worries.
You made me a promise, Yato!
You'd better find a way to fix me.
I'm sticking with you till you do.
Well, see you tomorrow!
Tomorrow, then.
Your name's cool. I like it.
Yeah? Thanks.
So, whose Regalia are you, anyway?
His name's Yato. He wears a tracksuit.
Yato, huh? Never heard of him.
He's such a minor god, he might as well not exist.
And you?
Me?
Not bragging or anything, but my god is totally major.
Yeah?
I serve one of the Seven Gods of Fortune.
I'm Lady Bishamon's Regalia!
Ah...
Wow. Seriously?
Seriously!
Ya-ho! It's me, Yato!
A soon-to-be major god and a snappy high school senior!
You? In high school?
The tracksuit won't be weird if I'm a student.
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"One of Her Memories."
That's not the only weird thing about you, y'know.