Hm. Yes. This one absorbs water the best.
Hope you don't mind, tree.
Your sap is what I need.
For making pills, there's none better.
So. We meet again, Kugaha.
Ah. Hello, Norry.
Don't call me by that name. I don't like it.
Really? What should I call you instead, then?
There are plenty of options.
You have quite a sense of humor.
By the way, that Yato fellow. I paid him a visit.
And? Your conclusion?
I think he'll be useful.
What's going on? Those two usually don't act so serious.
Yato, I need to talk to you.
Oh, yeah? About what?
Oh, no! Are they breaking up?
Has Yukki finally had it with Yatty?
Try not to cry for him. Yato deserves this.
I have no doubt he brought it on himself.
I...
Go on.
I... I think
I think I made a new friend!
Aw! How sweet!
Oh? Good for him. That's wonderful!
Is this his first friend as a Regalia?
Are they about the same age?
I don't know how thrilled I am about this.
The kid is just too easily distracted.
I'm relieved to see that Yukine is
thriving, even with a subpar master.
Maybe he looks to Yato as an example of what not to do.
Well, good for Yukine.
Who does this friend of his serve?
Oh. Good question.
As on the ball as ever, I see.
Do you always have to insult me, Tomone?
You know it's Mayu now!
And I'm not insulting you, just stating the truth.
Anyhow. What an excellent development.
Yukine had a rough time of it at first.
He seemed like a rather troubled young man.
No kidding. He's got father issues of his own.
His own issues?
Rend!
Great job! It only took one hit!
Revert, Yuki.
She's right, that was a good job.
I can tell you're really
Hey! Listen to me when I'm praising you!
Sorry! I'll listen later!
Where are you going?
To see my friend!
Don't forget about your homework, Yukine.
I'll do that later, too.
That punk. Ditching his master.
Aw, just let him go.
You finished your subcontract work for Lord Tenjin.
Don't call it that, okay?
We helped him. Helped him.
Sure, sure!
Just look at him. He's so happy lately.
Suzuha!
Hey! How are you?
Sorry I'm so late.
Don't worry about it. You're the one helping me out.
How 'bout I get you my master's autograph as a thank you?
Nah! That's okay!
What's your master's name again? Lord Yato?
I'll have her make it out:
"To Yato and Yukine, with love!"
Uh, no, seriously!
I'm good.
Aw! Don't be like that!
If he'd ever heard of Yato,
he wouldn't be suggesting that.
Wow. Your master gave you all of this?
Sure. All the fertilizer and seedlings I want.
Man! You've really got it good, you know that?
My stupid master never gives me stuff.
He actually stole money from me once!
A real jerk move, but I got back at 'im!
You guys are close, huh?
How do you figure that?
My master is totally amazing, but she's got lots of us.
Including her super-talented go-to team.
Kuraha, the divine beast. Akiha, the knife.
Karuha and Kazuha, the handguns.
Yugiha, the great sword. Kinuha, the whip.
And Tsuguha, in charge of defense.
Jeez, that's a lot.
Of course, there's also the Blessed Vessel and exemplar.
Kazuma holds them all together.
Blessed Vessel, huh?
They're all elite soldiers ready to
rush into battle at a moment's notice.
Together, they're the ultimate team of
Regalia for the ultimate god of war, Bishamon!
They're the top, but the master is
still really nice to all the rest of us.
Even with so many, she treats us like family.
That's the sort of god she is. Powerful and kind.
Sounds like a great master.
I can tell you really respect her.
Of course I do!
But, considering how many Regalia she
has, I haven't been called up in years.
Oh.
Hey, I know! You wanna see something cool?
It's huge!
This cherry tree was uprooted during a typhoon,
and it got sick. I've been taking care of it.
The hollow's finally growing roots again. See?
That is cool! You did this yourself?
I did have a little advice from an expert.
This is a pretty big tree, too. It must've been tough.
I guess. A friend and I made a promise, though.
That we'd see its blossoms together.
Oh. Another Regalia?
No, actually.
She was a living person, but she could see me.
How long ago was this?
It's been about 30 years now.
The flowers around here are so big and pretty!
Are you the one who takes care of them, mister?
These are sunflowers.
And those are morning glories.
Not bad! You know your flowers, kid.
Don't call me kid! I'm Tomoko!
Okay, Tomoko. What's this red one here?
A doodle-doo!
I don't think so. I'm pretty sure
these flowers are called hollyhocks.
Cock-a-doodle-doo! Cock-a-doodle-doo!
The flower garden here is always so pretty!
Are you the one who looks after them, mister?
Hello, Tomoko!
Huh?
How do you know my name? Have I met you before?
These flowers are so beautiful every year!
So, is this your garden?
Tomoko's grandmother lived nearby. So
she came to visit every summer vacation.
A butterbur cup, and a thistle basket!
You're really good at remembering flower names.
Is there anything else you remember?
Doodle-doo!
But she could never remember me.
She only ever came to visit during the summer.
But one time, she said she wanted
to see the cherry blossoms with me.
So we carved a promise into the tree.
I haven't seen her since.
That's how it goes.
The living forget us so quickly.
But, I'm hoping, at least, she remembers this cherry tree.
That would be enough for me.
What are you doing coming in through the window?
Well, if I came in through the
door, Daikoku would make me do chores.
Then do some! Don't you owe them that much?
Forget that for now.
Did anything happen with you today?
I've had a pain here for hours.
It's none of your business.
Please don't give me that. Just talk to me.
I don't think either of us want a
repeat of what happened last time.
Fine. It's about Hiyori.
Hm?
She's a living person.
When she gets older, will she forget us?
You falling for her?
Shut up! It's not like that.
I didn't think much about her at first.
She was just someone who seemed handy to have around.
But...
What are you waiting for?
Then I can't be friends with you anymore!
I'm so relieved! I'm so glad you're both okay!
She's more than that.
She always tries so hard to help us.
But, it seems like a waste of her time.
What do I matter? I'm already dead.
I might as well never existed.
Why do so much to help somebody like me?
I mean, really. Why bother? What's the point, anyway?
She's gonna keep getting older, isn't she?
She'll go off to school, get a job.
Someday, she'll get married.
She'll keep changing, and I'll always be the same.
That's fine, really.
I knew it would be like that.
I was hoping that we would stay friends.
But... But what if she forgets us,
and doesn't even remember who we are?
Sorry. Does it hurt?
Eh, don't worry. It's better not to hold it all in.
You just cry all you need to.
Seems like being around her might be hard for you.
You gonna quit studying?
No, I'm not. I don't want to quit.
Even though this might be my cherry tree.
Your cherry tree?
It's hard to explain.
By the way, Suzuha's having a blossom viewing
party soon, and he invited me to go to it.
Suzuha? That's your friend?
Uh-huh. He's one of Bishamon's Regalia.
It's taken root beautifully.
Hi, Doctor.
It's going to bloom just fine this year.
Thanks to all your hard work.
Well, thank you. But, I just did what you told me to do.
So, all sad and alone again this year?
Wha...?
How long are you going to keep this up?
For decades? For centuries?
I mean, surely it's obvious by now.
She forgot you a long time ago.
And she isn't the only one, is she?
How long has it been since Lady Bishamon
called your name? Years now, right?
Even your master has forgotten you.
That must be pretty depressing.
You're totally alone in the world.
There's nothing for you here. Why stay?
A name has disappeared.
That would only happen if one of my Regalia died.
But how?
It's unwrapped. I wonder what Suzuha was thinking.
You can't just leave it exposed.
He knows better than that.
Jeez.
Hold on a sec. I'll help you.
I hope he shows up.
You even made food for us. I wonder why he's not here yet.
Suzuha...
So he's one of Lady Bishamon's Regalia, right?
And that's not a problem?
It's really no big deal.
He's actually never even heard of Yato.
And I was told I should just
"run along now and play nice."
Like I'm a five-year-old or something.
Now I get it.
He's a lot more worried about Yukine than he lets on.
Which explains all these texts.
We're gonna have a blossom-viewing
party in the spring when it blooms.
You can come if you want.
Really? I'd like to.
You might forget. It's not for a little while.
Don't say that. I won't forget.
Yato still hasn't fixed my body.
And I've got a ton of stuff left to teach you.
Keep studying with me, okay?
You hungry? Should we eat now?
That sounds good. Just give me a minute, okay?
Hm?
"If you have some leftovers, don't be greedy.
"Remember gods gotta eat, too." And send!
Quit being a dirty sneak!
You wanna say something? Say it to my face!
Was that a tracksuit I saw?
Hmph.
Did he follow us here or something?
Oh, who knows?
Never mind that idiot, Yukine.
I'm hungry. Let's eat our lunch.
Suzuha told me he's been taking
care of that cherry tree all this time.
Wow.
It means a lot to him. That's why I don't get it.
He should be here now.
The flowers. Was it Suzuha?
This is bad. Suzuha hasn't come back.
Don't cry about it.
You know crying makes the master hurt.
Do you think a Phantom got him?
Can you help me?
Of course, my lady.
The three of you spend a lot
of time with Suzuha, don't you?
Do you know where he might be?
No, I'm sorry.
Everything's just fine, my lady.
There's nothing to worry about.
Okay, thanks.
Tsuguha? What happened to your hair?
Nothing, my lady.
Please, you seem shaken. Has something happened?
No, of course not! I'm just being silly.
Getting upset over a bad haircut!
I hope it didn't affect your health at all.
Well, I'm all better. I should get going.
She's taking more medication.
She seems so melancholy and run down lately.
Veena.
Why are we gathering so late at night?
It looks as though every Regalia's been summoned.
Ah. What's going on here?
Is this what I think it is?
We are holding an ablution tonight.
Know that I do this on my own authority, as your exemplar.
Our master has no knowledge of it.
The Lady Bishamon has been blighted.
Which means one of us has been
corrupted, and thus, brought her harm.
A Phantom must have manifested on the
body of the one responsible for the blight.
I ask you to show yourself.
All right.
Then we'll have to inspect everyone.
Please cooperate. For our lady's sake.
Dr. Kuga, if you will?
All clear. Next.
All clear.
You're clear, Aiha.
You're clear, too.
Well, I examined everyone.
Not a Regalia among us seems to be tainted.
Are you satisfied, then? Are we done?
Actually. There's still one left.
You haven't been checked.
Ah. Of course. You're right.
Well, that's easy enough to remedy.
Uh...
There! Feast your eyes!
Dr. Kugaha! There are ladies present!
Pristine, isn't it?
Kinuha! Stop staring! Cover your eyes!
But then who has blighted her?
I don't know.
But I can't believe you suspected us.
I'll agree that she has seemed exhausted lately,
and no one can blame you for being concerned.
But don't forget your responsibilities
as our master's exemplar, Kazuma.
We can't afford to have you
distracted or suspicious of us.
When we see your confidence
begin to waver, it shakes us all.
What's going on here?
My Lady Bishamon!
Oh, err, we were just
The blight is gone. But how?
Wait. So he had it wrong the whole time?
I'm glad Lady Bishamon is okay, but I
can't believe Kazuma had so little trust in us.
I knew it.
It's not much, but it's stormy here.
So, what happened? If it's what I suspect...
You really reek of dog. Did you kill him?
It isn't good to be so suspicious
and mistrustful all the time.
Such traits can prove fatal.
Especially for denizens of the Far Shore, like us.
Wouldn't you agree?
Who are you?
Oh, nobody special.
Just someone who wanted to meet the great Yato in person.
Not gonna give me a name?
What for? I'm just an ordinary Regalia.
Do you really need my name?
I'll ask a different question.
Why don't you tell me whose pet you are.
There's some real fire in you, isn't there?
That said, Lord Yato.
It doesn't matter how many petty
wishes you grant. You're a nobody.
No one will ever remember you.
I bet you must live in constant fear.
Without a Regalia, what are you?
Just a pathetic excuse for a god!
Did your master teach you to greet
an unarmed person with a Borderline?
That's really horrible manners, you know.
You don't have a single shrine, but you're that powerful?
You must have a particularly strong tie to the Near Shore.
Bonds with the Near Shore can be fleeting.
Also remarkably fragile, as I'm sure you're aware.
Ephemeral. I think perhaps that's
the best way to describe it, don't you?
I hope we'll meet again sometime, Lord Yato.
And please, until we do, try not to fade away, all right?
That's no problem! I'm not gonna disappear!
Not as long as there's someone out
there who still... remembers who I am.
Well, it looks like somebody taught you a lesson.
Oh, yes.
I think Yato's exactly what I've been looking for.
Everything is falling into place perfectly.
The Regalias' bonds are already
unraveling and growing hollow.
Many are ready to fall with only the slightest of nudges.
Bishamon is known for being a violent god of war.
Unfortunately, she is no longer
living up to her reputation.
Like it or not, you're going to help me, Yato god.
Oh, really? It's happening?
It is. The end is near for Bishamon.
Very near, indeed.
Can you tell me how to solve this equation, Mayu?
Of course I can! I do serve the god of learning, you know!
Great, thank you!
I think I'll call you Lady Mayu from now on!
On the next Noragami Aragoto: "False Bond."
You've never once called me Lord Yato!