Hm...
Hello, it's me.
Can you come over?
That's right. Lab #4.
I've got something interesting to show you.
Okay.
A smell?
But I didn't smell anything like that.
It's like a shark in a way.
Hm?
Smelling the scent of blood and
rushing to the scene of the crime.
Using each and every sense to track
down the perp and grab hold of them.
Closing in with rows upon rows
of the sharp teeth of evidence,
and not letting go until the perp gives in.
Hmph.
That's being a detective.
I really don't think that's a good idea.
You know there was a murder at this aquarium.
Should we really have "Operation: Rekindle Love" here?
I guess not.
Ugh, aw bummer! Look, it's starting to rain!
Huh? Really? We should run home!
Wait a sec! I thought I told you not to run!
What's wrong with running?
Ah.
No way! What the heck was my
cellphone doing inside my hood?!
Sorry...
I was trying to figure out where the perp had
put the cell phone to record the movie, and well...
I completely forgot I had put it there in your hood.
What're you gonna do about it?!
My Dad just got it for me!
No! Don't worry!
I'll buy you a new one! It'll be an even better one, okay?
You suck!
Something bad always happens when I spend time with you!
When we went to the states, all
you did was work on cases there too!
Okay, okay. Then...
I'll take you somewhere else.
How about we go to Tropical Land?
What's Tropical Land?
Where is this wonderous dream land...?
It's new! I heard they're
almost done building it in Tokyo.
And I'm sure there won't be any cases getting
in the way at an amusement park, you know?
If you're the one paying for it
all then I guess I don't mind going.
Huh?!
We should totally go if win the Tokyo karate tournament!
How about it?
Uuh...
Wait a second, I remember you
being the runner up last year.
And, didn't the upperclassman who won
the tournament retire from the karate club?
That's a promise, right?
Hmph.
Huh...?
It's not like I get that much allowance, you know?
And if you're gonna buy me a new cellphone,
make sure to put a Sea Slug Man strap
that they sell at the Beika Aquarium on it.
Yeah, yeah.
Also!
What? You're telling me there's more?
Well, I guess that's all for now.
Gee, thanks...
Ugh, it's raining so hard!
The forecast was way off today.
I'll have a... What he's having.
Really? You don't have to check the contents?
Hmph.
If this infos been faked, we'll just
have to take your life as recompense.
Doesn't stop me from checking on my end, at least.
Suit yourself.
Okay, confirmed.
Thank you for waiting.
So, have another job lined up?
Hm...
You know, I'm gonna at least need an
outline of what the next job's gonna be like.
How about this?
There's been a rat sneaking around lately.
It's been sniffing out info on the Organization.
Uh...
Well?
Oh. That's the first I've heard about it.
I see.
So, my next job is figuring
out who the rat is. Is that right?
No need.
We already have a hunch of who's
been sniffing around the place.
Er...
Oh.
Huh, this is actually a pretty good drink!
What's in it? Does this cocktail have a name?
It's Rum.
Cointreau, a little bit of lemon juice...
Huh?
"XYZ"...
A drink called, "This is the End."
Well, gotta go! Uuh...
Let me know if another job comes up!
You sure about this?
Just letting him go like that?
We both know that he has to be the rat for sure.
Yeah.
Don't worry about it.
Hmph.
It's a cocktail that signifies the end.
It's me.
Understood. Now get out of there.
Heh.
Alright then boss, what should we do?
You know, about the gun-smuggling data?
Doesn't matter.
We should continue on as planned.
Have you prepared enough cash?
You know we have to be sure they
understand how serious we are about this deal?
Yeah. But the whole thing could be a set up.
I wouldn't worry about that.
We can sus them out even after we've made contact.
Yeah, that is true.
Besides...
Huh?
Hmph.
That place is way too important to just give up on.
Hm... Huh?
Yes?
Oh, Shinichi!
Ran? What is it? It's way too early for this.
What are you talking about?!
It's already 11! Eleven!
Wait, seriously?
Ugh...
I'm coming in.
And? What are you doing here?
It's Sunday, you know.
So, you did forget after all.
Hmm? What did I forget?
Don't ask me what you forgot!
When I told you I didn't have karate practice
today, you said, "Then we should go buy your cellphone."
It was all your idea!
Er... Oh, sorry! I completely forgot!
Come on. You were up all night reading
a mystery novel again, weren't you?
Hah, you caught me.
Uh...
Just hurry up and get changed already.
In the meantime, I'll cook you
up something to eat for breakfast.
You haven't eaten yet, have you?
Oh. Thank you.
Look here! Just don't forget the Sea Slug Man strap, okay?
Roger!
Huh...
Hm?
So hey, remember how that car exploded near Beika Harbor?
It was on the night that we went
to the Beika Aquarium last week.
Yeah?
Did you find out what happened?
It looks like they still haven't figured out who did it.
You're right. That's kind of scary.
Don't worry. I'm sure it'll be solved soon.
Japanese police are amazing, you know?
Uh-huh. You're just trying to
say you're even more amazing,
because they come asking you for
help when they can't solve a crime.
Got that right!
Uh...
Can't you just be a little modest?
I'm joking! It's a joke!
Alright, are you ready to get going then?
Sure.
Mitsuhiko! Mitsuhiko!
Pass! Pass!
Ayumi!
Wah!
Ah! Uh...
Hmph!
Are you ready, Genta?
Ready!
Dah!
It's super easy.
Aww!
You almost made it, Ayumi!
Okay, so now it's my turn to kick!
Yah!
Woah!
Come on Genta! Where were you aiming that kick?!
Hehe... Sorry, sorry.
Sorry!
Hm?
Hey, would you get that ball for us?
Hup!
Woah... So cool!
Are you a soccer player?
Yeah, I used to be one. Catch!
Woah!
Wow, thank you so much!
Bye-bye!
I bet if we had a friend who was
as good at playing soccer as he is,
we'd become really good players too!
Totally!
What if you hadn't quit the soccer club?
Maybe you would've been a
member of the Samurai Blue by now.
Really? In 11th grade?
Why not?
Besides, the only reason I started playing soccer,
was to build the athletic skills
that are expected of a great detective.
After all, Holmes used to practice fencing, didn't he?
He's a fictional character...
Yeah, but he's a famous detective
known by everyone in the world over!
Uh...
That may be true and all, but...
He's the coolest!
He's always calm and composed,
He's wise and sophisticated, and his skills
of observation and deduction are unbelievable!
He's even a master violinist!
The famous Sherlock Holmes, created
by novelist Sir Arthur Conan Doyle,
is without a doubt, the greatest
detective the world has ever known!
Hmm...
Huh?!
Aah! Somebody get him, he stole my purse!
Hm.
Huh.
Somebody help!
Move it!
Woah!
Excuse me, please.
Please let us through!
Huh?
Ah...
Who the hell are you?
Haido High 11th grader, Hina Wada!
Isn't she...
Hey, Ran! Come on! You and I have got to help.
Uh-uh. It's okay, she's got this.
Huh?
Damn it! Gettin in my way? You're gonna get it!
Oh? You're gonna use a knife, huh?
Okay then, I guess I'll just have to take you seriously.
Karate?
Mhm.
Oof! Woaaah!!
Ugh!
Hehe.
Huh..?
Hmph!
Hm. Want some more?
Wow, looks like she's pretty strong, huh?
Mm-mm.
Stop it!
She's not pretty strong. That girl is strong.
Her first encounter with her life-long rival,
was unavoidable, as she pursued
mastering the martial art of karate.
They met in the spring time,
when Ran Mori was 16 years old.
Sonoko!
How about that?
What are you doing narrating my life like that?
And it's not even spring yet, geez!
Oh come on! I'm just creating the atmosphere!
It's not even my first encounter with her either.
Oh, so you do know her.
Yeah! I've faced her many times.
Never mind that, Ran. Come over to my place!
But we're already on our way to the...
You guys can go on a date some other time! Let's go!
Wait, Sonoko!
Huh.
I'm home!
Welcome home, Lady Sonoko.
Well, come on in you guys!
Nice to see you again!
Welcome, Miss Mori and Mister Kudo.
So today, we have the Puru Fuwa Cheese Tart,
a confectionary that I ordered from Hokkaido.
Huh? The one that you have to wait 3 months for?!
Yup! Let's eat it together!
I'm so excited!
Is it okay to eat something like
that right before your tournament?
Don't blame me if you get fat.
It's fine!
My upperclassman Kazumi's coming
over to help me practice a bit tomorrow.
In fact, I'll even double my routine if I have to.
Jeez.
You have such a nagging husband.
Hey, what do you mean husban—
What is it, Sonoko?
Oh! You have guests? I'm sorry!
Welcome back, Sonoko.
Just barging in like that. How impolite.
No problem! Such youthful energy!
This must be your daughter?
Yes! Our daughter Sonoko.
Nice to meet you.
How unfortunately embarrassing.
She lacks awareness of the heir
to the Suzuki Financial Group.
You've got my sister for all that.
It's about where your heart should be.
Ah yes, that's right! And standing
behind my daughter are her friends,
Miss Ran Mori, and Mister Shinichi Kudo.
Uh...
You know, Ran's father used to
be a detective in the police force,
and he now makes his living as a private eye.
Perhaps you could discuss your case over with him?
Uh, well...
There's a case?
Mr. Sewa will be holding a party this weekend,
so they came all the way here to invite us.
However, unfortunately, we
won’t be able to make it ourselves.
We have a briefing that same
day that we simply cannot miss,
for the upcoming jewelry exhibition at Beika Museum.
Oh, the Black Star one Uncle Jirokichi was talking about.
Yes.
But according to Mr. Sewa,
he received a startling message,
warning him to cancel his party.
And that if he didn’t, one of
his party guests would be murdered.
I see...
You can count on Mr. Shinichi
Kudo to handle something like that?
Huh?
If you must know, Shinichi is
a renown high school detective,
who has helped the police solve a
number of seemingly unsolvable cases!
I hate to say this,
but he's way better at it than Ran's father.
That's for sure.
I think I could be of some help to
you if you'd let me take on this case?
Well, that is quite encouraging!
Just to be safe,
we've already increased the number of security
guards we'll have present at the event that night.
I don't think we need to ask a
detective for help at this point.
Well, I guess it's about time that we got going.
Alright?
Yes.
Woah! Ah!
Watch out!
Woah!
Hmph.
My God! What do you think you're doing?!
Pay proper attention!
Uh... Well, we've been spared, thanks to you.
Thank you so much, miss.
Sure!
Nice save, Ran!
Thank you so much.
I certainly hope you didn't get hurt?
No, I'm fine!
I inherited a very sturdy body from my father!
Oh. Did what I say bother you?
I didn't mean it.
Well, you see, the Mori family is quite the family!
Jeez, Sonoko...
Mr. Kudo?
What seems to be wrong?
Nothing! Everything's fine.
Oh, this is amazing!
It's made of a super lightweight
material that was developed
by the Suzuki Financial Group's
very own textiles division!
And the sleeves are a bit narrower and less
baggy, yet still quite easy to move around in.
I may not look it, but I'm quite
the martial arts fanatic, you see.
Are you really sure it's okay for me to have this?
Well of course!
I may have played a tiny part in
its design as well, just so you know.
Wow, you did?!
Yep!
You can even call me couturier
Sonoko if you like my style?
With that karate outfit...
you're set to win the tournament for sure!
That's the power of love!
Well the thing is...
What's the matter?
She's not allowed to use that outfit at the tournament.
What's that?! Really?
That's right, each tournament has
it's own different outfit regulations.
I'm really sorry, Sonoko. But I'll
wear it during practice and do my best?
I guess it can't be helped.
So then you'd better win that
tournament! Or I will be upset!
I'm sorry, Mrs. Suzuki.
Oh, it's fine!
We can't be there to cheer for you.
But do give it your best shot, alright?
Right!
We still didn't get a chance to go buy your cellphone.
True. Well, I'm gonna go buy a
few things for dinner and head home.
Okay. We'll go get your cellphone next time.
Mhm!
See ya!
See you later!
Aah!
Shinichi! I forgot my wallet at your place!
Seriously?
Shinichi!
Hey, Shinichi?
I found my wallet so I'm gonna go.
Okay.
I still can't believe how many books you have in here.
And that all of them are mystery novels.
I guess your father was able to became a world-famous
mystery novelist thanks to reading all of them, huh?
And you became a mere mystery junkie.
I resent that.
Not to mention your beautiful
mother is the legendary actress,
Yukiko Fujimine!
I'm so jealous.
It's not as great as it looks, you know.
Hey, I bet I know who your first love was?
It was your mother, right?
What?! No!
Okay then, who is it?
Mm... urgh... Dah!
Well if you must know, my first love was...
Yes, she was..?
I'll tell you who my first love was...
Hm?
Woah?!
What in the world are you doing?! Doctor Agasa!
So tell me, how's your homework coming along?
I thought it was about time
for you to start feeling drowsy!
How was it? I bet this woke you up!
Don't move around so much, Doc!
Ow! Sorry about that.
So what kind of experiment was it this time?
So, you want to know after all!
Not really.
Well, since you insist, I'll tell you everything about it!
Ta-da! It's a personal rocket!
"Ta-da?" Come on, really?
Once I've finished perfecting this baby, traffic
jams and the like will finally be a thing of the past!
And not to mention, I'll be a millionaire!
Hmm.
But isn't that thing kind of dangerous?
I mean it's basically a missile, am I right?
What're you talking about?! I consider
safety first with every last thing I make!
This incident was a fluke!
Huh? Woah!
Shinichi!
Aah, Doc!
He's hopeless.
What!?
Come on, shut up! Stop nagging me already!
It's not like I want to go with you, either!
But here's the thing. Ran wants...
It's only natural that parents
go cheer for their children.
What I'm trying to say is...
Isn't there something more important you
should consider doing, before deciding on that?
I'm sure you don't have any jobs
chalked up for this month, either.
Argh! Don't go making assumptions!
I've found 3 this month already, you know!
Three?
Doing what?!
You're a great detective who
spends his time looking for lost dogs!
No, not dogs! Cats! Don't you mock me!
The other day, I stomped into a place...
I'm home!
... when actress and producer
were having an illicit affair and...
What? That's a case! No, it's totally a case!
I'll call you when dinner is ready, okay?
So stuck up! Aren't you just deceiving them?
But that president...
I can't figure out why he went out of his way to choose
such a place so full of people to carry out the deal?
He underestimates us.
He thought choosing a place like that
would prevent us from making a scene.
And if he just happened to bring a companion along,
that crowd would make a great cover for escape.
Then maybe it is a trap.
Bourbon mentioned the president was
also seen hanging out with the Deisankai.
Wow, Bourbon huh?
That guy sure knows how to sniff things out.
Well, even so,
since we know about it, there won't be any issue.
We'll just have to kill him first.
Haah!
Aah!
Ah! Woah!
Yah!
Woah!
And, stop!
She did it!
Alright!
Blue, high kick, one point!
And blue wins!
Hm, haha!
That was fantastic! Ran is amazing!
At last Mr. Mori! She made it to the finals!
Ha, she'll make it hands down!
Ran wins when it counts, just like I do!
There's no way she'll lose in the finals!
I pray she didn’t also take after you in
getting carried away and dropping the ball.
What's that?
Well, since Ran's also my daughter,
I'm sure there's nothing to worry about.
Ran! Go for it at the finals!
Ah, where is he? Just like him to disappear.
Yes, yes, I understand.
Alright then Inspector. Right away.
The Kumite Women's Section Finals will now begin.
Red, Haido High School, Hina Wada.
Here!
Blue, Teitan High School, Ran Mori.
Begin!
Hah!
Ah!
Ah! Hmph.
Hmph.
Hah! Yah!
Hup!
Ah!
All right, all right! That's good, keep it going!
Stay calm Ran, please!
Stop!
Huh?!
Red, middle kick, two-point! Ready. Begin!
Hah!
Gah!
Stop!
Hey! Ran, what are you doing?!
Ran! Focus! You can do it!
Focus! Focus! Focus super hard!
Focus hard!
Waah...
Huh?
Oh...
Hm... Huh?
Shinichi?
What?
There's... a... case...
There's a case?
It's just never ending cases... Just cases, cases,
and more cases!!
Damn you...
You crazy deduction freak!!!
Hmph.
Heh.
I wish you'd just drop it already.
I don't have time to waste on
your fruitless investigation.
Please, no need for you to be rude.
There's no mistake here. Trust me on this,
the perp in this case is one of the people here tonight.
Then, why don't you find that
"perp" right away and arrest him?
We know who it is.
Huh?
We already figured out who the perp is.
There you are Mr. Kudo! We were waiting for you.
I'm so sorry. I know I'm a bit late.
Who does this young man think he is?
He can't possibly be here with you!
Hmph. Have you forgotten?
We met just the other day at the Suzuki residence.
Hm? At the Suzuki's?
If you must know, Shinichi is
a renown high school detective,
who has helped the police solve a
number of seemingly unsolvable cases!
A high school detective, eh?
Here are the facts as we know them,
Mr. Yamazaki, president of Beika Bank, was
murdered in the guest room on the third floor.
I happened during a party that
was being held here earlier tonight.
Hmm...
The victim's death was caused by a knife wound.
The door of the room was completely locked,
and the key to the room was in Mr. Yamazaki's pocket.
The only thing left open, was the
veranda window that faces the garden.
Therefore, the perp had to have made
their way through the veranda window,
and killed the resting Mr. Yamazaki.
Then they fled the scene of the
crime the same way they entered.
But when they checked, there weren't
any shoe prints under the window.
Besides, all the other rooms surrounding the
guest room were properly locked up for the night!
That's true that, there were no shoe prints under
the window, and all the other windows were locked.
There was no way to get to the open window.
If that's the case, then how did...
Hmph. He flew in from the outside.
What?!
That's ridiculous.
Come now.
Are you being serious, Kudo?
Of course, he didn't come flying down from the sky.
There's a small window diagonally
across from the window in question.
The perp jumped from that window
all the way to the guest room window.
That's nonsense!
Those two windows you're talking
about are at least 5 meters apart!
That's utterly impossible...
On the edge of the roof leading to the small
window is a ledge, though a very narrow one.
If you use that as a foothold and move towards the wall,
it's only a meter or two to the veranda.
And so, the perp is someone who already knows
the unique structural characteristics of the house.
And is someone who could easily walk around
the place as they please without suspicion.
Alright, well get on with it then!
Who was it who killed President Yamazaki?!
That would be...
You right there!
Hm?
Mr. Yamazaki's best friend,
as well as the head of this household...
Takanori Sewa!
D-Don't be ridiculous!
That'd be impossible with this foot!
The cat's out of the bag!
Hmph.
Just what do you think you're doing?!
Ah... Father...
Mr. Sewa...
Hmm..? Huh?
Oh my dearest... It's your foot.
It's something I noticed when I
met you at the Suzuki residence.
You used your broken foot to try and stop
yourself when your wheelchair malfunctioned.
I bet that foot has long since healed, am I right?
Argh... Damn it!
Wait, hold it!
Uh-uh, you're not getting away!
Yes! Goal!
Well, thank you for your kind
assistance yet again, Mr. Kudo.
Don't mention it.
If another tough case should arise,
you can rely on the great detective Shinichi Kudo!
Hey, so have you heard?
That high school detective solved another case!
Yeah! He's so fantastic!
This young detective is being hailed as a
bright new hope, for Japan's law enforcement agency.
Ah! Guh...
Ow! What was that for?
Idiot. Stop being so cocky about it.
Ran, are you upset or something?
Not really.
Thanks to your great detective
work my Dad has less to do now.
So no. I'm not upset at all.
Uh...
Okay, but it's not my fault nobody's
giving your dad any cases to work on...
It's because of his mediocre skills.
Ah... haha...
See what did I tell you? I'm not the least bit angry!
Why would I be angry?
That's the captain of the karate club for you.
Jeez.
Everybody makes a fuss over you being a great detective,
but you're nothing but a deduction freak.
But just look at all these fan letters!
Everybody else seems to like the
fact that I'm a deduction freak?
Whatever.
I don't mind you getting moonstruck over girls,
just make sure you can narrow
it down to your favorite girl!
My favorite girl?
Huh...
Just unbelievable.
Hm...
What?
Woah!
What are you doing staring at my face like that.
Um... you know, nothing...
If you keep snooping around all of those cases,
you're gonna wind up in real trouble!
Perhaps.
But why even become a detective?
Huh?
Since you love mystery novels so much, why
don't you aspire to become a novelist like your dad?
Hm... I don't want to write stories about detectives.
I want to be one.
Ah...
Hmph.
I'll become the 21st century Sherlock Holmes!
Huh...
The more difficult the case the more excited it makes me!
The thrill of cornering the perp who's
used up all their tricks! The ecstasy!
I can't get enough!
Once you have a taste, you just
can’t stop! It's an addiction.
Huh...
See you, Ran!
Uh... wait, Shinichi!
Hm?
You remember the promise you made for tomorrow, right?
What promise?
It was your idea!!
You said so yourself that you'd take me to
Tropical Land if I won the prefecture tournament!
Really? I said that?
Just forget it.
I didn't really want to go with you anyway!
Go have fun with the girls that write you fan letters!
I was only joking! Come on, please!
Don't get mad. I do remember, okay?
Tomorrow 10AM, Tropical Land.
Hehe...There's no way I'd forget.
And don't forget that you promised to pay for everything!
Urk! I did promise that didn't I.
Hey, hold on! Wait up, Ran!
No way!
We're back in Japan for the first time in forever,
and we have to leave without seeing our son first?!
I went through all this trouble to disguise
myself because I wanted to surprise him, and now...
Hmph! It was totally in vain.
Well, we're only in Japan to
retrieve some old reference materials.
We'll just have to save our disguises... for another time.
Besides, we'd only be getting in their way,
if we revealed ourselves now.
Mmmm!!
I wanna do that, so I can see his angry face!
Wah!
Thirsty? I got you a drink!
Oh, um thank you.
Come on, this way!
Hey! Where are we going, Shinichi?
Don't worry about it! Just follow me!
Ah, uh...
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one, zero!
Heh.
This is totally cool! Wow!
Uh...
You do like things like this, don't you?
Mhm!
Uh!
Heh.
But do you wanna know what the most
amazing thing about Sherlock Holmes is?
He was such a great detective that when
he first met his assistant Dr. Watson,
he could tell just by shaking his hand
that he'd been in Afghanistan as a medic!
Just like this, watch!
Huh?
Let me guess. You're in a gymnastics club, right?
Huh? How... could you possibly know that?
Who's that? Is he someone you know?
I don't think so?
I could tell from your hand.
Huh?
A woman who has this many blisters on her hand,
must be a gymnast who performs on a horizontal bar.
Uh, yeah but... You can get blisters from playing tennis.
Well actually,
the wind was blowing pretty hard outside,
and I was able to catch a short
glimpse when her skirt blew up!
The bruise I saw on her upper thigh is unique
to people who practice on uneven parallel bars.
Huh?!
It's important for a detective to always be observant.
Can't let anything out of sight!
What in the world are you talking about?
Besides, it's cheating if you already
knew the truth before shaking her hand!
Hey, you!
Huh?
You better not even think
about making a pass at my friend!
Uuh, er...
Are those two friends of yours?
Well, yeah...
In that case, would you like us to change places with you?
Oh, no no! It's fine!
Yeah we sure wouldn't want to get in the way of those two!
Hmm...
You see...
The thing is Ran, I've always had feelings for you...
Really? Me too, Shinichi.
Shinichi?
Shinichi!
Gah!
Shinichi, hurry up!
Huh?!
Huh? Oh, yeah! Right!
Thank you for riding!
Please watch your step as you exit!
Oh that was so scary!
Let's go on it again!
And then after that, Holmes decided to...
There's room for two more!
So that's basically what Conan Doyle
was trying to say about Sherlock Holmes.
And when you think about it that way...
I’ve heard more than enough
about Holmes and Conan Doyle already!
So knock it off you deduction freak!
You don’t know... You don’t even know how much I've
been looking forward to coming here with you, Shinichi...
I don’t understand how come you never notice how I feel.
Uh...
Ran...
Oh, hey, you know? Actually, I also um...
Huh?
You're so silly.
What are you getting so flustered about?
Come on, couldn't you tell I was lying?
Damn it!
Aw, you took it seriously?
If you fall for easy stuff like this,
you'll never make it as a detective.
Okay! Now departing!
See you all later!
Just so you know...
Huh?
I'm glad I'm here with you! I really am.
Huh?!
Ah...
Woo!
Hmm. So we're not seeing any action, huh?
Come on, let's go. We're pulling out!
Orders are to withdraw.
Hm?
What's wrong? Wanna ride that?
Boo!
Wait what? Water?
And it's salty?
Huh?!
Ugh, woah! What is this stuff?!
Huh? Woah!
What the heck is going on?!
Hope you all had a great ride!
Please watch your step as you exit...
There must have been an accident!
Call an ambulance!
Call the police, too!
Why, why, why?!
Oh why, Kishida?! Why?!
Shinichi.
Ah, what a tragedy.
A truly terrible accident. No
reason for us to stick around.
Hold it! This was not an accident!
Not at all. It was a homicide.
And the person who did it was
also riding on this roller coaster.
The perp is amongst the seven of us!
Really Shinichi?
Hmph, I won't play along with all this crap!
Excuse me, please let us through! Excuse me!
Excuse me! This way, please Inspector.
Oh, Kudo! And Ran, you're here too!
Oh hey there, Inspector Megure!
Kudo?
No way! That kid must be the famous
high school detective Shinichi Kudo!
Yeah, the one who's solving one cold case after another!
Well maybe he can find the murderer!
Check it out, it's him! It's really him! It's Kudo!
I wanna see just how he does it!
Hm...
Oh, well now...
Seriously?
I see.
Interesting. There are no signs of defects
or malfunctions with the roller coaster itself.
Based on the circumstances, it's unlikely a suicide.
Hmm...
And that's exactly it, Inspector.
That's why it's clearly a homicide.
Okay, but who's the perp, and how did they do it?
Inspector.
Hm?
Hm.
We'll have to keep those who were
on the coaster around for questioning.
Everyone else, please clear the area while we investigate.
Please leave the area!
So this roller coaster is an eight-person ride.
Excluding you and Ran from the suspect pool for now,
that leaves five other riders.
The victim's friend, Suspect
A was riding in the first row.
Likewise for Suspect B.
The victim's girlfriend was riding
in the third row, right next to him.
We'll label her Suspect C for the time being.
The men in black that were riding behind the victim,
we'll label them Suspects D and E.
Now this is where it starts to gets tricky.
Because of the safety bars, none of
them had any real freedom of movement.
The only one who could've kill the
victim was the person seated next to him.
That would be his girlfriend, Suspect C.
Actually, the men behind him could've done it.
Hey, we've had enough.
We don't have anymore time to play
along with little detective game of yours.
Uh, hey Bro...
We're really sorry. Please bear with us a little longer.
What's going on... What's with the icy look in his eyes?
He looks like he wouldn't even hesitate to kill people...
Wh-Who on earth is this guy?
Inspector, sir!
Hm? Did you find something Chiba?
Yeah, we found something alright! A murder weapon!
No, lies! I haven't seen that thing before, it's not mine!
Aiko, what happened?! Why would
you do such a horrible thing?
I'm telling you! I didn't kill him!
And here I thought you and Kishida were hitting it off!
So why?!
Believe me! I really didn't do it!
See there's your perp! That broad
over there's the one who did it!
So we're free to go now right, Mr. Officer?
Oh, wow, they found the perp even
faster than I expected. That's surprising.
I knew there was something weird about that lady.
A lover's quarrel huh?
Pretty darn scary.
That's it, I've heard enough. Take
her in for immediate questioning.
Please come with me.
N-No! This can't be!
And just to cover all our bases,
we'll be checking the identities of everyone
else that was on the ride while we’re at it!
Do you guys have a problem with that?
Please wait, Inspector.
Hm? What's the matter, Kudo?
I'm certain that she's not the one who did it.
Then who, Shinichi?
Really now?
Hmph.
While on this roller coaster, the person
solely responsible for killing Mr. Kishida...
...is you!
Huh?!
What?! But how can that be?!
You can't be serious!
You saw the bloody knife that
was in Aiko's bag, didn't you?
You can’t expect me to believe that his
head was severed with a knife like that, can you?
Especially not with the strength of a woman.
And besides, if she really were responsible,
she had about a million chances
to get rid of the murder weapon.
There was no reason to go out of her way to
wrap it up and hide it in her bag like that.
Huh...
Which means, you had to sneak the
knife into Aiko's bag beforehand.
That way, you could easily shift the blame to
her, and no one would suspect you in the slightest.
Where did you come up with an idea like that?!
I was sitting in the very front!
I wasn't anywhere close to him!
Are you crazy?! How could I have
chop his head off from over there?
Besides, you just said so yourself!
That a woman isn't strong enough
to sever a person's head like that!
Hmph, that's true. That is exactly what I just said.
However,
it is possible if you use the roller coaster's
speed with some piano wire or a steel ring!
Inspector, I'd like to ask for your fellow officer's
assistance in recreating the crime scene in question.
Well alright. That shouldn't be too much of a problem.
Okay, everyone!
I will be playing the role of the perp, Miss Hitomi.
And the Inspector will play the
role of the victim, Mr. Kishida.
Mhm.
Mm...
Now first, before we start lowering the safety bars,
I'll take my seat and put
something like a bag behind my back.
Then, I'll lower the bar. Now before I start,
I'll take the bag out from behind me and create a gap.
See? Now I can slip out easily.
Next, I'll pull out a murder weapon I prepared beforehand,
like some piano wire or a steel
ring with a hook-like attachment.
I'll climb up onto the safety
bars, and reach out behind me,
at which point I'll loop the victim's neck.
Of course, this was all done in the pitch-black tunnel.
Then, all I'd need to do is
take the hook attached to the ring
and connect it onto the roller coaster's rail.
The speed and power of the roller coaster would
then be used to chop the victim's head off at the neck.
Th-That's ridiculous!
How could I do that on a moving roller coaster?!
Because, you are an experienced gymnast.
Perhaps others wouldn't be able to.
But you have a great sense
of balance, and could do
something like that easily
even on a moving roller coaster!
Alright, stop! We've heard enough of your lies!
Then tell me. What happened to your necklace?
The one you had around your neck
before you got on the roller coaster.
Where exactly is your pearl necklace?
Ah!
You switched out the string that was
holding your necklace together for piano wire,
and hid the hook that you would
later attach to it inside your bag.
Hold on a second! If things
went down the way you say they did,
wouldn't it be easier for those two scary looking guys
that were sitting right behind Kishida to pull it off?!
No, you’re wrong. They’re definitely not the
perps, no matter how suspicious they may appear to be.
How do you know?!
I don't know why they were on the
roller coaster in the first place.
But, it's strange how they changed
their tone the minute the police arrived,
like they wanted to get out of here as soon as possible.
If they were the perps, they would have
realized what would happen when the ride ended.
Uh...
After all, the perp was aware of
one thing. The victim would die.
And that's why she cried on the ride.
Mmf! Huh?
Wait what? Water?
Not much time passed between the
victim's death after exiting the tunnel,
and when we got back to the station.
In other words, the only person who would
shed tears while still on the ride is the perp.
They'd be the only one who knew.
So then what you’re trying to tell us is
that you saw Hitomi crying on the roller coaster?
How exactly can you prove that?!
The trail of her tears is irrefutable proof.
Unless you're doing something
like riding a roller coaster,
those teardrops wouldn't streak sideways.
It was...
It was all his fault! It's all because he dumped me!
H-Hitomi, don't tell me that
you... You were dating Kishida?!
I was! We were in love and together,
way before we met the rest of you interlopers in college!
But Aiko...
To think someone like her!
That's why... So that's why...
Going on the roller coaster we rode on our first date,
using the necklace he gave me,
and framing it all on Aiko...
That why I killed him like this!
Later, a large amount of sleeping pills
were found tucked away inside her bag.
It seems as if she was planning on following
Kishida to her own death after the crime.
Two hours later, the necklace used to
commit the crime was found inside the tunnel.
The string had indeed been swapped out for piano wire,
and most of the pearls had scattered.
The setting sun shone upon the
remaining pearls, giving them a faint glow.
As if, they were large teardrops.
Hey come on, stop crying already!
How can you stay so calm through all this?
Well it's because I'm used to
seeing those kinds of crime scenes...
You know, like dismembered bodies and stuff?
That's horrible!
Woah, hold on! The sooner you're
able to forget it, the better!
You know, this stuff happens all the time!
No, it really doesn't!
Uuh... Um...
It's that guy...
One of the suspicious ones from the roller coaster.
You said incidents like that
don’t happen at amusement parks...
Sorry, Ran. Go home without me, okay?
I'll catch up with you really soon!
Wait, Shinichi!
Ah!
He's leaving.
Shinichi?
For some reason, at that moment I had a bad feeling...
A hunch that... I would never see Shinichi again.
I was certain of it...
Damn it. I lost track of him.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Mr. President.
There he is!
I-I came by myself as I promised!
Yes. I know you came alone.
Because I confirmed it while riding the roller coaster.
Hey, just hurry with the stuff!
Hold your horses. The cash first.
Fine then, there's no problem with that.
No way... That's like a hundred million!
Alright, we have a deal.
Hurry, just give me the film!
Film?
Here you go.
Thats every last negative and print that
can prove that your company was smuggling guns.
Now just try to keep yourself out of trouble.
Shut up!
Hmph, compared to what your organization does...
What we do is...
Hey! What the hell do you think you
know about our organization anyway?
Huh?
Gah! N-Nothing!
You do realize that we’re sparing your life
for the measly sum of a hundred million, don't you?
Well now that you are aware, shut down
your company and get the hell out of town!
All we want is to build a new lab on
that lot, got it? Nothing else to it.
R-Right!
Unbelievable... Seriously?
Ah...
That's enough playing detective for you.
Aah!
B-Bro!
Idiot. You let this brat follow you out here.
It's the detective... from the roller coaster!
Damn it! So should we get rid of him?
Not this time.
The cops are still all over the
place because of that murder earlier.
Well then, what should we do?
Heh. Let's see how this works.
These capsules are filled with the
Organization's newly developed poison.
They said the toxicology tests won't be able to detect it.
A drug that makes the perfect crime possible.
From what I hear though, it
still hasn't been tested on humans.
Hey bro, we better hurry.
Yeah.
Farewell, detective.
It feels like I'm on fire!
It's like my bones... My bones are going to melt!
No..! No...
No...
Hey, over here!
There's a dead body!
What?!
Heh... So, I died after all.
Wait! He's still breathing!
An ambulance! Get an ambulance!
I-I'm alive?
I see, looks like the drug doesn't work on humans!
How lucky can I get!
This is terrible.
He's bleeding from his head.
We found a kid.
Oh, the police?
There are so many of them.
Okay, I'll tell them all about
the evil deed that I just witnessed!
Hey, you'll be alright. Can you stand up there? Well, kid?
Huh?
Come on kid, are you alright?
Huh? "Kid?"
Who are they calling a kid? I'm in 11th grade...
What happened kid? Your head's bleeding.
Wounded? Ah, that's right!
I remember... That man in black
hit me in the head from behind.
Huh?
What?
Wh-What's with these clothes?
You must have been pretty scared, kid..
But don't you worry your little head. We're here now.
He lifted me up so easily.
Sir, we're taking custody of a boy found
below the Ferris wheel with a wound on his head.
We're take him to the medical now.
Uh, he looks about six or seven,
likely still in elementary school.
Elementary school? What?!
I'm home!
Oh! So you're back, Ran.
Aw jeez, Dad! You made another mess of the place!
Now this is exactly why you never get any clients,
and why mom Mom ran out on you!
Shut up. I'm just picky when it comes to clients!
By the way, where's that kid that thinks he's a detective?
I thought you were gonna spend the day with him?
Hm...
I'll catch up with you really soon!
I wonder what happened... Is he okay?
Aha! Trouble in paradise, huh?
Well, just let him be!
Those detectives are all a
bunch of good-for-nothings anyway.
But aren't you a detective?
It's just like I've been telling you!
I swear, I know what I saw! There was a guy who was
smuggling guns, and another was there blackmailing him!
But then their accomplice found me!
And whacked me on the back of my head!
Come on, kid. You've seen way too many cop shows.
I already told you, I'm not a kid! I'm in 11th grade!
What is this? Something's wrong...
I checked in with park security. There's no
record of any corresponding missing child reports.
The way they're acting...
Especially since he's been wounded.
These baggy clothes, and...
and my voice..!
Damn it, is that even possible?
No. Doesn't matter how impossible it may seem.
There is always only one...
What the...
Are you kidding me?!
Has my body really shrunk?!
That's why he doesn't want to go
home, and says whatever comes to mind.
It's looking more and more
likely that he ran away from home.
I guess we can contact headquarters for now, and
have the police daycare center take care of him.
What?! Daycare center?
Alright then, kid...
Huh? He's gone!
He must have run off through here!
You've gotta be kidding me!
No way I'm gonna let them put me in daycare!
Hey, kid!
Oh no!
There he is! That way!
Damn it!
Wait up, kid!
It's like I'm a criminal or something!
Ran!
All right! If I can get Ran to pick me up...
Ah...
But, with my current voice, and this body...
Damn it!
Ah...
That's right! I can text her!
Wait, there's no way to explain what happened...
If you keep snooping around all of those cases,
you're gonna wind up in real trouble.
Hm...
Take a look over there!
No... Damn it! Damn it!
Hey, this is Kudo. I can't come to the phone right now.
Please leave a message after
the beep and I'll call you back.
Oh, he's still not home yet...
Hm? I'm sure he's just out somewhere having dinner!
Probably with his famous novelist father.
What? Come on Dad!
Shinichi's parents have been living
in the States for the past three years,
and since then he's been living all by himself!
Oh yeah? Is that right?
I was right... Something did happen to him.
I'm going to Shinichi's house for a bit!
Huh? Hey! but what about my dinner?
To think I'd be out of breath, after running so little...
And then there's this body...
What the hell happened to me?
Hold on.
I remember now... Right before I was knocked out!
Let's use this poison that the organization developed.
From what I hear though, it
still hasn't been tested on humans.
Don't tell me... That poison I drank?
It can't be...
What in the world are you doing in
the middle of the road?! You damn idiot!
Watch where you're going, dumb brat!
"Brat," huh... How pathetic.
Ugh!
Urgh... Oh... wah!
Aw man! I can't even get into my own house now?!
Ugh...
And there's nothing I can do about it!
Hmph!
What? Oh no!
Ugh!
Ugh... Hm?
Huh?
Oh?
Oh! Doctor Agasa!
Ooh!
And who might you be?
It's me! Me! Shinichi!
Oh, how wonderful! So you're one
of Shinichi's little cousins, huh?
As a matter of fact, you look a
lot like Shinichi when he was little.
Of course, that's because I am Shinichi!
You know, Teitan High School, 11th grader,
Shinichi Kudo!
Hey are you home, Shinichi?
You've got yourself a guest out here!
Argh!! You've got to be kidding me!
Agh! Ow!
Oh! What's going on?
You alright little guy?
Well since you don't believe me, fine!
I'll tell you about you!
Huh?
Hiroshi Agasa, 52 years old!
You're my neighbor and an eccentric inventor.
You call yourself a genius,
but everything you make is junk!
Huh?!
You also have a hair sticking
out from a mole on your butt!
M-My butt?!
That's something that only Shinichi knows about.
Don't tell me Shinichi's...
telling everybody about my secret?!
I didn't hear about it. I'm telling you, I'm Shinichi!
I was forced to swallow poison that shrank my body!
Hm? A poison?
Shrank your body?
Yeah.
A poison?
Hmm...
Huh?
Hmph, if there really is a poison
like that, I'd be interested to see it!
Come along, suspicious brat! I'm turning
you over to the police, this instant!
Wait! Just give me a minute to prove it to you!
Look! You just got back from the
restaurant Columbo, after having dinner!
And, you were in a hurry to get back home!
Wh-wha-? How do you know that?!
Take a good look at your clothes.
The front of your shirt is all wet, while
the back of your coat is completely dry!
Huh?!
That proves you've been out in the rain.
And your pants have been splattered with mud.
What?
And there's only one road here that gets muddy.
The construction zone in front of Columbo!
You also have meat sauce on your mustache,
that's the exact same color as
the meat sauce served at Columbo!
Huh?! Uh...
Wait that must mean... No way!
Uh-uh-uh! It's elementary, my dear Agasa!
Shinichi! So then it really is you! But how would that...
That's what I keep trying to telling
you! I was shrunken down by poison!
Hmm... It's still not easy to believe.
Something like this shouldn't even be possible.
But you knew about the mole on my butt! Hmm...
Can you just let me inside my house?!
Wow, really? A gun smuggler, you don't say?
Yeah.
A couple of guys who were
trying to blackmail the smuggler.
So in order to shut you up,
they force fed you a poison pill?
Hmm... Oh!
Now I see! And because the poison was untested,
it must have had this strange side effect.
That must be why it shrunk your body like it did!
That's about right.
Look, since you're a genius and all...
Can you make an antidote that
will return my body back to normal?
Well, ehem...
You're asking for the impossible.
Without knowing the drug's
components, there's nothing I can do!
Oh man...
The clothes I wore as a kid fit me perfectly now.
So all I have to do is locate their hideout,
and find some of that poison!
Right, I might be able to make an
antidote if I had a sample... But...
Huh?
Shinichi! Don't tell anybody else
about how you've been shrunk down in size!
Huh? Why not?
Because you're still alive!
If the men who did this to you realize that,
they’ll stop at nothing to make sure you wind up dead!
Not only that, but they may go
after the people close to you as well!
Ah...
You got that? The fact that you are
Shinichi Kudo has to remain a secret we keep,
just between you and me! You must never tell anyone else!
I mean it! You can't even tell Ran, got it?
Alright... I understand.
Shinichi, are you here?
Ugh! If you’re at home, the least
you could do is answer your stupid phone!
And you left the door unlocked!
Oh no it's Ran!
Not good! Hurry up go hide!
Yeah, I gotta get out of here!
Hey are you in here? Doctor Agasa!
Wah! Hey there! Long time no see Ran, how are you?
Have you seen Shinichi?
Oh! Well um... He was just here a minute ago, but...
Uh well, he said something about, there's a case...
And ran off somewhere!
Urk!
Huh?
Uuh...
So, who's this kid?
Him?! Well, he's... that young man! Well he is a... Aah!
Aw, talk about shy!
Hey! Let me take a look at you.
Aah...
Not good...
Hey this kid, he's...
Aha...
Just so darn cute!!
Not bad... Hehe...
Whew!
Doc, who is this kid anyway?
Wah?
Oh, well... He's a very distant relative of mine!
So then, how old are you?
Uh, I'm sixteen... I mean...
Uh... I'm six years old!
Oh really? So you're in first grade, huh?
Uh... Yeah!
What's your name?
Uuh!
My name is uh... Well its actually, uh...
Well you see, it's uh...
Hmm?
Well it's kinda, unusual really... It's um...
Uh... Conan!
Huh?
Um yep! That's my name! Conan Edogawa!
Crap. What a slip of the tongue!
Conan? That's an unusual name.
Uh... my Dad's a big fan of Conan
Doyle... So that's where my name comes from!
You know you kind of remind me of Shinichi...
Doyle's fine, but he's still got some homework to do!
Hey Doc?
Why did you go with Conan?! It's
not like you were born in England?
I couldn't help it, okay? It was
just the first thing I thought of!
Hm?
Oh!
Ran, I um, hate to ask,
but could Conan stay at your place? He would be
no trouble, and he would only be there for a while.
You've gotta be kidding!
His parents are in the hospital
right now because of a car accident!
So they asked me to take care of him.
But seeing as I'm a guy living alone, I...
Well, I don't really mind, but I'll
have to talk it over with my father first.
Well, that's great news!
So you'll do it! Thanks so much!
Ouch!! Ow! Ah...
Hey! What if they're able to figure out
who I am while I'm staying over at Ran's?!
Will you just listen?
The men in black will eventually realize that your
body was never found, and that you may still be alive!
And when they do, the first people they'll
suspect is anyone seen staying at this house!
Okay but, what about at your house?
Don't you think it would be safe there?
For your body to return back to normal,
First you'll need to find the ones
responsible for your condition, right?
Well yeah, of course...
Ran's home is a detective agency, remember?
Hey wait, you're right! If I stay
there I might find some info on the perps!
My thoughts exactly.
Hm...
Hmm...
Excuse me, Doc?
Yay! I'd rather stay over at your place!
He's so cute!
If you only knew...
Okay then, Doc.
Make sure you tell Shinichi to call me when he gets back.
Right, I'll be sure to let him know.
See you later, Uncle! Bye-bye!
I'll see you later, uh, C-Conan! Hehe...
The rest is up to you to figure out, Shinichi.
I mean... Conan... Edogawa.
Hey so, Conan?
Hey Conan?
Huh..?
Oh! What is it, what did you say?
I gotta get used to this name.
Do you have a crush on anyone?
Huh?
Come on, there's gotta be
someone you like. At school maybe?
Who me? No...
Well I have a crush!
Huh?
Someone I really care for!
Hehe, I know who it is!
It's that Shinichi guy you
were looking for just now, right?
Hmph.
Huh?
That's right!
He's been a meanie since we were little.
He's a pretty cocky guy, and a total deduction freak
but when it matters, he's really reliable,
and courageous, and awesome!
When it comes to Shinichi, I like him a lot!
Um... Promise me, you won't ever tell him this.
Okay...
You're the only person I've told this to, okay?
You really can't tell Shinichi what I said!
I won't...
Well, this is my house!
It's like I just adopted a cute little brother.
I feel like I can tell you anything!
Ran...
Looks like Dad's home. Let's
introduce you to him. Come on!
Actually, Ran...
Huh?
Well, it's just that...
What is it?
The thing is, I'm really...
Yes! I did it!
Huh?
Woah-woah! Aah!
Ow! Uh...
What is going on, Dad?
I got one! I got one, I got one! I got a job!
I got my first decent client in six months!
Watch where you're going! Did you say you got a client?
Yeah, a rich family's daughter was
kidnapped! Supposedly it was men in black!
Men in black?!
Finally!
Huh? Wait, Conan!
You just wait, men in black.
I'm gonna find out where you
are and get a hold of that poison.
And once I'm back to normal...
I'll make sure everyone knows about your acts of evil!
And so, in order to gain information on the men in black,
I wound up staying at Ran's house,
where her father works as a detective.
And it turns out, he’s not exactly great at his job...
I couldn't just sit idly by and watch him fail,
so I used my own powers of deduction,
and Doctor Agasa's inventions,
to solve one tough case after another on Pop's behalf.
Don't tell me that Dr. Narumi...
Intended to die all along?
Ugh... Damn it, Narumi!
Conan you can't do this!
No Ran, let me go!
That music... What is it?
It's a type of code...
I can't believe it... He's still playing... In the flames.
You idiot.
There isn't any win or lose to deduction.
No top or bottom to it.
There's always only...
There's always only... One truth... Heiji.
Uh, Heiji...
Huh?
Have you ever...
Have you ever had to kill somebody before?
Huh?
You idiot...
A detective who has a perp cornered,
and is willing to just let them commit suicide...
...is no different from a murderer.
So therefore, when you exclude all impossibilities...
What remains, now matter how hard it
may be to believe, is the undeniable truth.
Didn't I tell you? That was your last chance.
Aah!
Ugh...
No, Masami!
Hurry up! Go call an ambulance!
And bring Pops! Go!
Okay!
It's... It's no use...
It's already too late.
Gotta save your energy! If you don't then you might...
Kid...
You're that kid? The one at the detective agency...
The Organization?
Yes...
A large one that's shrouded in mystery.
The only thing I learned, from
being at the low end of it...
...is that the organization's color is Black.
It's Black?
Yes, that's right...
The guys in the organization all wear...
...clothes that are black, just like ravens.
It can't be...
The men in black.
I'm counting on you...
Little Detective...
He's gone by many nicknames over the years.
"Lupin of the 21st Century,"
"Magician under the Moonlight."
However, there is one nickname in
particular that most people are familiar with.
A nickname?
A young novelist took interest in Phantom Thief 1412,
who lead global police forces on a wild goose
chase. He had them right where he wanted them.
That novelist saw the number
1412 and read it as follows...
K-I-D. Kid.
K-I-D?!
Wait, but that's...!
That's right. Phantom Thief 1412.
Better known as...
Kid the Phantom Thief!!
You know kid. You're no ordinary brat.
Conan Edogawa. I'm a detective.
Yeah. Right.
I'm heading over to a drama filming as we speak.
It's our last day of filming so I can go in
your direction when we're all wrapped up there.
And all I have to do is to make
sure that Pisco doesn't mess up?
I was already going to head over there anyway.
I have my reasons.
I've gotta go now.
I need to shake an FBI kitten that's on my tail.
I'll see you when I get there, Gin.
Hm.
Damn it! Move it! Get outta my way! Move!
Forget it.
But, we're so close!
You'll never catch up with
her. She's just the better driver.
But don't worry. I know where she's headed.
What? Where to?
To Japan.
Huh?
Conan Edogawa?
You know, the boy with glasses that I told you about.
You went somewhere in Beika-cho right, to someone's house?
You said you had something you needed to do there.
Right, Shinichi Kudo.
That's right. He lives at a detective agency near there!
So, tell me about the boy.
Well, he's kind of a weird kid.
He's surprisingly calm especially for a child.
He's rather mature.
I see...