‐Dammit.
When is this night gonna end?
‐It’s almost over.
Try and be patient.
‐If you go out now, Naraku
will find out that you lose
your demonic powers on
the night of the new moon,
and then you’ll be
wide open to his‐‐
‐All set.
I’m going.
INUYASHA: Kagome.
You better make it
back in one piece.
‐It’s way too quiet.
‐Father, Kohaku.
Tonight, I’ll finally get
revenge for our village.
Naraku!
Kilala!
Miroku, he’s coming your way!
‐I’ve waited for this, Naraku.
Feel the wrath of the
curse you set upon me.
Wind Tunnel!
What, Saimyosho?
‐Perish.
Impudent wench.
‐Naraku.
You’re going down!
I got him.
SHIPPO: Kagome, look out!
Transform!
‐Miroku!
‐Is that thing
Naraku’s true form.
‐Hey, Kagome.
‐Where’s Inuyasha?
‐Not yet.
‐Looks like we’re on our own.
We’ll have to do it without him.
‐Let’s go, Kilala.
‐OK then, Shippo.
Are you ready?
‐Yep.
S‐Sure you don’t wanna
put this off for a while.
‐Oh, come on, Shippo.
‐A barrier!
‐All right, we’re going in.
‐Hey, pretty good job, Shippo.
The ribbon’s a nice touch.
Give it a rest.
Oh no!
He’s coming for us!
Oh!
‐Don’t run away!
‐I’m still just a kid, you know.
‐Aim for his legs and maybe
we can stop him from moving.
‐Kilala.
Dive under his belly and‐‐ Huh?
This is hardly the time.
You’re depraved!
MIROKU: I couldn’t help myself.
SANGO: Keep your
hands to yourself.
‐Argh.
What the hell do they think
they’re doing out there?
I can’t stand it anymore.
‐No.
Wait!
You mustn’t go out, Master Inu‐‐
‐Shut up.
‐Smushed again.
‐Huh?
Kagome!
‐Inuyasha.
Inuyasha!
‐Look down there.
‐The moonless night is ending.
‐He made it.
‐Sorry to keep you
waiting, Naraku.
[music playing]
‐I’m the one you
really wanna fight!
‐Now, Lord Inuyasha!
Use the Tetsusaiga
to break the barrier.
‐Right.
‐Now, if you’ll excuse me.
‐The barrier is disappearing.
‐Yeah.
I knew Inuyasha could do it.
‐Miroku.
Take the right.
‐Consider it done.
‐Inuyasha!
‐Kagome.
Where’s the jewel
shard on his body?
‐Just a sec.
On his back.
‐Gotcha.
Die!
‐Inuyasha!
‐Stay out of the way.
‐Hey, watch it!
NARAKU: Inuyasha.
Become one with my body.
‐Inuyasha!
‐My sacred suture didn’t
work on him either.
‐Get your filthy body off of me!
‐Keep moving or you’ll wind
up getting caught again.
‐I know that.
‐Try as you might, your
attempts are in vain.
‐Says you.
I’ll hack you into
pieces sooner or later.
‐Sango!
‐Wretched fools.
‐Prepare to die, Naraku.
Wind Scar!
‐It’s over, Naraku!
‐I can feel my heart
beating in my chest again.
‐Naraku.
He’s dead.
‐My sister, Sango.
‐Did we do it?
‐Did we finally defeat Naraku?
Hey, what’s wrong, Miroku?
‐Shippo.
‐Hm?
‐Look.
Take a good look, Shippo.
‐Huh?
‐Miroku’s Wind Tunnel
has disappeared.
‐Kanna, What exactly
do you expect
to find in a place like this?
‐Kagura, what is
it that you wish?
‐I thought would be obvious.
Freedom, for I am
the wind itself.
Hm?
Kanna?
‐Your wish will come true.
‐Don’t you understand?
I have my freedom now
that Naraku’s dead.
Hm.
‐I’m at a loss.
How ever do I get to Mount Fuji?
It’s so dark, I don’t
know which way to go.
[sigh]
‐Huh?
KAGOME: This feels great.
It’s been ages since
we relaxed like this.
SANGO: Kagome.
‐Hm?
SANGO: What do you plan to
do now that Naraku is dead?
‐Don’t know.
Well, I guess I still have
to look for the sacred jewel
shards.
Remember, we didn’t find
the shards that Naraku has.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): When
all the shards are found,
what will I do?
What reason will I have
for returning here?
KAGOME: Sango.
‐Huh?
KAGOME: We have to look for
your brother, Kohaku, too.
‐With Naraku gone, I
wonder how he’s doing.
‐Don’t worry.
He’ll be fine.
If we keep searching
for the jewel shards,
we’re sure to find
Kohaku sooner or later.
‐That’s right.
We’ll all help
you, don’t forget.
‐I appreciate that.
‐Oh.
Young maidens.
Celestial maidens bathing.
‐Excuse me.
You there, sir.
‐Who’s there?
‐Would you care to explain
what you are doing here?
‐Give it a rest, Miroku.
Can’t we even bathe in private?
‐You have it wrong.
s only standing guard
to protect you from danger.
Nothing more.
SANGO: The only protection
we need is against you!
‐Wait, Sango!
Don’t be rash!
‐What was that?
‐Inuyasha, you pervert!
Sit!
INUYASHA: I was
just trying to help.
KAGOME: Yeah, right!
Help yourself to a peek!
‐Thank goodness I was spared.
INUYASHA: Like
I’d wanna see you.
‐A mirror?
‐To meet nevermore.
Tears of sorrow overflow
deep within my heart.
What good, this potion of life?
All is but dust in the wind.
‐So, Naraku has died.
Now all living creatures in
this world must be eliminated,
and eternal night shall be mine.
‐Who are you?
Name yourself.
‐I am the princess of
the heavens, Kaguya.
Behold.
The dream castle of
the pentacle mirrors.
Kagura, your freedom is
but a fleeting illusion.
‐Heh.
So what if it is?
What about it?
‐I shall show you
everlasting freedom.
I know your true wish,
and I can grant it.
WOMAN: Something for us
to do to pass the time.
TEACHER: TO meet nevermore.
Tears of sorrow overflow
deep within my heart.
What good, this potion of life?
All is but dust in the wind.
This is the verse
composed by the emperor.
I will never see
Princess Kaguya again.
The tears of sadness
overflow and set
me adrift on a
sea of loneliness.
What good would the
potion of immortality be?
I have no use for it now.
That, class, is what he
was trying to express.
The emperor orders
his vassals to take
the potion of immortality
to Tsuruga, to the tallest
mountain in Japan, and burn it.
At that time, the
mountain was called
the Mountain of
Immortality, or Fushi,
from which the name
Mount Fuji derived.
That’s all for today.
Remember, class.
Your reports on the tale
of the bamboo cutter
are due next week.
GIRL: Kagome.
Kagome.
Class is over.
GIRL: All rise.
Thank you, Ms. Yamada.
KAGOME: More homework.
Just what I didn’t need.
‐We’re in junior high.
Why do we have to write a
report about a dumb fairytale?
‐Then again, the
author Murasaki Shikibu
wrote that Tale of
the Bamboo Cutter
is the forerunner of all novels.
‐So it’s like a
classic of classics.
‐Hey, what do you think
of Princess Kaguya?
She finds suitors
who wanna marry her,
then gives them super hard
tasks to prove their love.
In the end, she dumps them all.
Even the emperor gets dissed.
Then she goes back to the
moon and doesn’t marry anyone.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
That’s right.
Princess Kaguya went back to
the moon and never returned.
I wonder how long
I’ll be able to keep
traveling between the
two dimensions of time?
‐Hey, speaking of
suitors, your guy
sure likes to woo you with
all kinds of presents.
‐Huh?
‐Well, I wonder what you’re
in for today, Kagome?
[bell ringing]
‐Kagome, over here!
‐Oh, look.
Speak of the devil.
‐You’re getting healthy.
You’ve been at
school a lot lately.
‐Yeah, feeling
better all the time.
‐Drink this.
It’ll build up your
strength even more.
‐Gee, thanks.
‐I was wondering
about this Sunday.
Are you free?
How about going to the fair?
And this time, you
better not cancel on me.
SOTA: Sis!
‐Huh?
‐You got a sec?
‐Sota, what’s the matter?
‐It’s Inuyasha.
He’s‐‐
‐Is something wrong?
‐Naw, not reality.
See you later.
[barking]
‐Now, what about Inuyasha?
‐Well, he was at the house
until a little while ago,
but he’s disappeared.
‐Why weren’t you watching him?
You weren’t supposed to
let him out of the house.
He’s bound to attract all kinds
of unwanted attention dressed
up in that gaudy red outfit.
‐Sorry, I couldn’t help it.
‐Would you mutts be quiet?
Sit!
[thud]
‐Hm?
‐Huh?
‐Inuyasha.
What are you doing here?
‐What are you talking
about, Kagome?
You took so long getting
back, so I came for you!
BOY: He’s got long white
hair, and horns, too!
INUYASHA: Hey!
What are you doing?
GIRL: I heard it was a man.
KAGOME: Hiding.
Or at least trying to.
GIRL: And then the man
took the boy’s candy.
INUYASHA: Ha ha.
Very funny.
‐I thought the girl was
gonna give him chocolate.
‐So what took you so long?
‐I want to spend time here.
Is that such a big deal?
‐We ain’t got the time.
We have to go find the
sacred jewel shards.
Got it?
Besides, let me
remind you that it’s
your fault that the jewel
shattered in the first place.
‐I know that!
‐No you don’t!
‐Nonstop fighting.
It never changes.
‐Once we’ve got
all the shards, you
can come back here
any time you want.
‐Oh, gee.
How very kind of you.
You can’t do a thing without me.
INUYASHA: What are
you talking about?
‐How about some precious
memories of how dumb
you two look?
INUYASHA: What was that?
Get down, Kagome!
‐KAGOME: Stop it!
INUYASHA: Iron
Reaver Soul Stealer!
KAGOME: Knock it off!
‐There they go again,
making a scene.
‐Not finished?
That’s the crystal
from the dragon’s neck?
‐Interesting.
A demonic aura has
replaced Naraku’s.
I will discover whose.
FIVE LAKES OF FUJI
LAKE YAMANAKA
‐Oh, arrow of mine, with
power pure and immense
to slay the dragon, do you
a good deed fast and swift.
Grasp the crystal in its neck.
FIVE LAKES OF FUJI
LAKE SHOJI
KANNA: I ventured to see if
what I had heard was true.
But this jeweled
sprig with leaves
so real twas nothing more
than an empty promise.
‐Three more, [inaudible].
‐Which one should
we go after next?
‐He who wears cloth woven
from the fur of the fire rat.
Inuyasha.
‐Fine.
INUYASHA: What are you doing?
‐Might as well keep these
pictures of us together.
Look.
‐Hm.
‐There.
It’s all done.
Here.
‐What’s this for?
‐A locket.
Promise you’ll
never take it off.
‐Yeah?
How come?
‐Uh‐‐ Cause it’ll grant
your wishes, for one thing.
‐Right.
‐Oh, yeah.
Believe me, it works much
better than the sacred jewel.
‐Liar.
I wouldn’t be caught dead
with a thing like this.
‐What’s wrong with it?
Hmph!
You are a jerk.
‐Huh?
What did you say?
Huh?
‐What’s wrong?
Inuyasha?
‐That scent‐‐ it couldn’t be!
‐Now where are you off to?
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
This is Naraku’s scent.
I’m positive.
He’s still alive.
‐Inuyasha, here at last.
‐Huh.
You again, Kagura.
You’re here to avenge
Naraku’s death, I assume?
‐Naraku?
Ah, yes.
How soon we forget
those we detest.
Well, he’s out of my life now!
‐Then why the visit?
‐Inuyasha!
‐Dance of Blades!
‐Kagura!
‐Dance of the Dragon!
‐Inuyasha!
‐Stay away!
‐The cloth of the fire rat.
Now I have it.
‐What?
Huh?
KAGOME: A full moon?
KAGUYA: the white hot flames
of my love for you cannot burn
this cloth of fur.
My raiment, sleeves dried of
tears, now on this day I dawn.
‐What’s that?
[laughter]
‐Who’s there?
Show yourself!
‐My name is Kaguya.
I am the ruler of eternal night.
‐Kaguya, is it?
What do you want with me?
‐Inuyasha!
‐Get back!
I don’t like it.
She’s dangerous.
‐I can see your desires.
Your very deepest desires.
Your true self, where
your dark heart rules.
You’re but a despicable beast.
[growl]
‐Quit your jabbering and
come on out of that mirror.
Wind Scar!
What happened?
Huh.
Fine, then.
I’ll just have to stick it
to you right in the heart.
‐Dance of the Dragon!
‐Backlash Wave!
‐What?
Kanna!
KAGUYA: The fool.
‐What’s that?
Huh?
[scream]
‐Sit!
[laughter]
‐Inuyasha, how
pathetic you’ve become.
Requiring the
protection of a mortal?
‐Inuyasha!
Inuyasha!
KAGUYA: Is it the fate of
man to live with these fears
all their lives?
That girl‐‐ the flow of time
is different around her.
‐Sure you just
wanna let them go?
KAGUYA: I have what I came for.
FIVE LAKES OF FUJI
LAKE MOTOSU
Could you have but known that
it would burn so swiftly,
this raiment of fur,
you would not, then,
have sat with such
little show of concern.
‐So you defeated Naraku.
‐Yes.
‐Your late father
and grandfather
must be proud up in the heavens.
‐I hope so.
‐Now what, my son?
What will you do
from this point on?
‐Now that I have
defeated my arch enemy,
there is only one more
duty that I desperately
need to take care of.
To ease the hearts of
the beauties scattered
throughout this land, and
with my body and mind,
I will‐‐ Sango isn’t here.
What am I thinking?
‐What ails you?
‐It’s a woman,
whose jealous wrath
seems to haunt my every thought.
Will I ever recover
from this fear, monk?
[laughter]
‐Come, my boy.
Let me read your palm.
Hm.
Oh, dear.
You have only
three days to live.
‐Only three days?
‐Actually, I’m only kidding you.
I have something
for you, Miroku.
Your grandfather,
the monk Miyatsu,
left this last
testament with me.
I was told to give it to the
descendent who defeated Naraku.
‐I wonder what everyone’s
doing right now?
You know what?
I think we should
hurry home, Kilala.
[hiss]
‐What’s wrong?
Kilala!
[grunting]
‐Give us the sacred jewel shard!
[scream]
‐Looks mighty tender,
that human flesh.
‐I’ll devour his thighs.
‐And I, his eyeballs.
‐Kohaku!
‐My lady.
‐Tell me, what happened here?
‐Many demons came, and the
villagers were all slain.
‐Demons?
‐Take this.
The head priest entrusted
me to protect it.
The stone bowl of Buddha.
Guard it well.
It’s what they want.
‐Are you sure you
want to give it to me?
Can you be sure that
I too am not a demon?
‐You’re no demon.
And you’re not evil.
I can‐‐
SHIPPO: Inuyasha,
are we just gonna
leave without Miroku and Sango?
‐So, where do you
sense the jewel shard?
‐I don’t know about this.
You’re still too wounded
to be up and around.
‐Quit talking, and get pointing.
‐I see what’s going on here.
If I’m not mistaken,
you’re still
angry cause you lost to Kagura.
Who’s asking for your opinion?
‐See?
What did I tell ya?
You’re gonna explode.
INUYASHA: I told
you to keep quiet!
[smack]
[scream]
‐Oh, I knew it!
You are angry!
‐Inuyasha!
‐Hmph.
HOJO: What do you want with me?
‐Do I have to spell it out?
Leave all your
belongings, and go.
‐I am on an important
mission, my good men.
Can’t you steal
from someone else?
‐When we’re done with you‐‐
‐Step aside, ladies.
‐Hey.
Hold it.
How dare you pass by without
bowing your head in respect!
‐That’s not wise.
Inuyasha’s in a bad mood today.
‐Don’t make me laugh.
You want to see a bad mood?
I’ll show you a bad mood.
‐I’m serious, you guys.
Better apologize while
you have the chance.
INUYASHA: Too late.
‐You want trouble?
You got it!
‐Thank you for
coming to my rescue.
I am truly in your debt.
‐Huh?
It’s Hojo.
‐Hm?
‐Hojo is my name.
Akitoki Hojo.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
Could he be an ancestor?
‐Here’s a small token
of my appreciation.
‐Thank you.
‐It’s quite tasty,
and it’s good for you.
Please try it.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
A health nut.
Now I’m positive
he’s an ancestor.
‐Oranges, anyone?
Oh!
‐This is beautiful.
What is it?
‐Ah, our precious
family heirloom.
‐Well, what you
mean, your heirloom?
‐It’s the Hojo family
heirloom, the celestial robe.
‐Celestial robe?
As in the famous one?
‐Exactly.
Now, if you’ll excuse
me, I’m in a hurry.
Farewell, and thank you again.
‐What an idiot.
He’ll never survive
in these times.
MIROKU: Help yourself.
‐How kind.
Thank you.
‐The full moon has not
waned in a long time.
‐Don’t I know it?
My friends have been up
partying every night.
‐This very same phenomenon
occurred 50 years ago, too.
‐Oh, you don’t say?
MIROKU: The grandfather,
the head monk Miyatsu,
put a spell on an
evil demon that
made the full moon
appear night after night.
‐You’re talking about
Naraku, I suppose?
‐No.
He’s dead.
‐But not missed.
Doesn’t his death mean the
wind tunnel in your right palm
is gone?
‐Yes.
It does.
I’ve been thinking,
Hachi, about going
to my grandfather’s grave.
[sigh]
‐Is that why you summoned me?
What’s the problem?
It’s not like the nightly
full moon bothers anyone.
‐Grandfather Miyatsu
wrote in his will,
she stops time without
care or remorse,
and destroys all living beings.
So you will come along
with me, won’t you, Hachi?
‐Why take this raccoon dog?
What use would he be?
‐Rest assured, Master Mushin,
Hachi has unquestioned loyalty.
‐Huh.
Yeah, as if.
Who’d take on such a
dangerous job, anyway?
‐Are you saying, then, you
will not heed my request?
‐Ha!
Why should I be scared of you?
You’ve got no wind tunnel!
‐Hm.
Let’s take a short
walk, shall we?
We’ll be right back.
Won’t be long.
‐Go east on him, now.
‐What’s the matter?
Come.
‐Doesn’t know what he’s in for.
MIROKU: You ingrate!
I’ve been good to you, demon!
A simple favor
That’s all I asked!
Hachi has kindly
agreed to accompany me.
‐Excellent.
A safe journey to you both.
‐Come.
Yes, sir.
Give the word, and I
shall lead the way.
‐Another full moon?
How could that be?
Huh?
What’s this?
[groan]
‐Huh?
‐Kohaku?
‐Uh‐‐
‐You feel well enough to get up?
‐Where am I?
‐The Village of
the Demon Slayers.
Our village.
‐Our village?
‐Kohaku, you still
don’t remember
much about what
happened, do you?
‐I’m sorry, Miss Sango.
‐Huh?
It’s OK.
No need to be sorry.
‐Huh?
SANGO (VOICEOVER):
Naraku is dead, yet
you’re still not
freed from his grasp.
You’re still tormented
by the painful memory
of killing Father
and the others.
‐Sister?
‐Huh?
Kohaku?
What did you say?
‐Sometimes that word will
suddenly come back to me.
And the pain comes.
Like my heart is being crushed.
‐It’s OK.
Don’t try too hard.
The memories will
come to you in time.
Kilala?
[hiss]
‐Kagura!
Leave him alone.
He’s not going with you again.
‐All I want is the
swallow’s cowrie shell
he possesses, nothing more.
We were both freed from Naraku’s
hold, so let’s be friends,
shall we?
Hand it over without quarrel,
and I’ll spare your life.
‐Kohaku, get my Hiraikotsu.
‐Kay.
‐Dance of the Dragon!
‐Get inside!
[screaming]
‐Kohaku!
‐Thanks for the gift.
[scream]
‐How’s your leg?
‐Never mind me.
What about the shell?
‐What is it?
This shell?
‐I guard it.
If it gets into their hands‐‐
SANGO: What will happen?
KOHAKU: The spell
will be broken.
‐Master Miroku?
This gave‐‐ is this the one?
‐Yes.
It’s the grave of my
grandfather, Monk Miyatsu.
‐Excuse me.
You there?
Tell me, monk.
Did you know Master Miyatsu?
FIVE LAKES OF FUJI
LAKE SAI
‐Time has passed
swiftly as I have
waited to see the
shell you promised.
They say that I wait in vain.
Could this be so?
‐One more object remains‐‐
the stone bowl of Buddha.
[laughter]
‐Think there’ll be
another full moon tonight?
‐Well, works just fine for me.
‐Spectacular!
I’ve never tasted
anything so delicious.
‐So, tell me, Hojo,
Which way are you headed?
‐I cannot reveal that to
a stranger such as you.
Ah?
I’m on my way to Mount Fuji to
throw the robe into the crater.
‐Throw what robe?
You don’t mean the
celestial robe, do you?
‐Exactly.
The robe was entrusted to the
Hojo family generations ago.
It previously belong to an
immortal celestial being,
they say.
Since then, we have cherished
it as our family treasure,
until one day a
very high ranking
monk came with this warning.
When the full moon shines
for many, many nights,
throw the robe into the mouth
of the Mount Fuji crater,
otherwise great calamity
will fall upon the land.
And these past several nights,
the moon has been full.
The monk’s prediction
has come true.
The robe must be destroyed
as soon as possible.
INUYASHA: What a story.
‐Huh?
‐If what the monk
said is actually true,
what kind of calamity
is supposed to happen?
‐I don’t really know.
Ah.
‐That’s right.
The moon and the celestial robe.
It’s the story of
Princess Kaguya.
Under the light
of the full moon,
celestial maidens came for her
and dressed her in her robe.
‐Did you say Kaguya?
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
She did reek of disaster.
That much I’m sure of.
‐The dead priestess who lives
off the souls of the departed.
You’re looking gloomy as usual.
‐Answer me, is this
all Naraku’s doing?
‐Are you still worried
about that rotting corpse?
‐He’s dead?
What’s the matter?
Won’t you accept it?
It’s what you seek, is it not?
‐You’re very
generous about this.
‐I’m not like you.
‐Such a creepy woman.
But I am indebted
to her, for now I
have my last sacred object.
And for that, I am grateful.
‐There is a
terrifying legend that
has been passed down
in this village.
One day, a heavenly being
was beating in a spring
by the village.
A man who saw her stole
the celestial robe
she had left hanging
on a tree branch.
‐Oh, yes.
I know that story, old man.
The man who stole the robe
and the celestial maiden
were married.
‐The story in the
village is different.
The being whose
robe was stolen grew
mad with fury, and
consequently slew one innocent
villager after another.
By a stroke of luck, monk
Miyatsu came upon this village
and sealed the maiden
inside a mirror
known as the Mirror of Life.
‐I can’t help but wonder if she
was indeed a celestial being,
or was she merely a
demon disguised as one?
‐I do not know.
But I’ve heard that the robe
stolen by the man was genuine.
HACHI: Does this celestial robe
still exist in this village?
MAN: No one knows
where it is now.
‐What about the Mirror of Life
in which the maiden was sealed?
‐It was placed on the
altar with a divine sprig
in the Forest of
Illusion, at the Shrine
of the Mirror of Life.
FIVE LAKES OF FUJI
LAKE KAWAGUCHI
FEMALE VOICE: I hope to find
the gleam of the fallen dew,
but nothing can I see.
Why did you go yonder
to Mount Ogura?
‐The moon is truly
beautiful when
seen through the eyes
of a physical body.
‐I’ve kept my promise.
Now let me have this true
freedom you speak of, Kaguya.
‐Not. yet.
‐Hm?
‐There is one more
thing I require of you.
‐Hey, here it is here.
The book says that Princess
Kaguya made all her suitors
undertake rigorous
tasks, and there’s
mention of cloth
from a fire rat.
‐Hm?
‐You see?
It shows the jeweled sprig, the
crystal from the dragon’s neck,
the stone bowl of Buddha,
the swallow’s cowrie shell,
and the cloth of the fire rat.
That’s why Kagura came
after your kimono.
‐They make a nice,
cozy twosome, huh?
‐Alas, unrequited love.
‐So what’s your problem?
Are you in love with Kagome?
‐When I first glimpsed Miss
Kagome through the steamy mist,
I thought she was a
celestial being from heaven.
‐Hm?
Ah.
I get it.
You were the spying pervert.
‐Hush, hush, hush!
Don’t ever say that aloud!
‐Hm.
All right, but you have to
be my servant from now on.
‐Huh?
‐You know, maybe this
Princess Kaguya in the legend
didn’t really want to
return to the moon.
‐Huh?
What are you talking about?
‐A shooting star!
Hurry, make a wish.
Inuyasha?
Tell me, do you still want
to become a full demon?
‐Yeah.
Of course I do.
‐You’re pretty strong
already, don’t you think?
‐Be quiet, will ya?
I’m going to become
a full fledged demon.
I’ve already made up my mind, so
just quit bugging me about it,
would ya?
‐I’ve been thinking,
there’s nothing wrong
with staying the way you are.
I mean, why not
stay a half demon?
To be honest, I like you
just the way you are.
‐That’s ridiculous.
‐What’s so ridiculous?
Can’t you be a little serious?
‐What is it now?
‐Inuyasha?
You just‐‐
‐Come on.
Spit it out.
‐Hey.
What’s that?
‐Strange.
How can cherry blossoms
fall in this season?
‐What‐‐ what’s wrong?
KAGUYA: The time has now come.
Behold the robe from heaven
to drape upon my shoulders.
And for you, it is but a
deep sadness that I feel.
‐Thanks for saving me the
trouble of hunting you down.
‐Not the two of you again.
What poor luck I have to
come across such fools.
Where is the celestial robe?
‐What are you talking about?
‐There it is.
‐You ain’t gettin’ it!
[chanting]
‐What?
‐You won’t interfere.
‐Inuyasha!
‐What’s happening?
‐I wondered why
you were so weak.
Now I see.
You’re merely a half demon.
‐That a problem for ya?
‐Inuyasha!
‐Kagome!
‐Yes.
There it is.
The celestial robe for
which I’ve searched.
[chanting]
‐Run, you fool!
‐Kaguya!
‐Such impudence.
A sacred arrow.
Interesting.
‐Release Inuyasha now.
‐Get out of here, Kagome!
‐Just go ahead and try it.
‐It’s your funeral.
[chanting]
‐Inuyasha!
‐Kagome!
‐Watch out!
‐Kagome.
Kagome!
‐I’m so thankful‐‐ you’re
all right, Inuyasha.
‐Why did you do that?
Why didn’t you stay away?
‐It’s no big deal.
And besides, you’re always
saving me, aren’t you?
‐Kagome.
Kagome!
[laughter]
‐Damn.
Let me go, you creepy witch.
If Kagome dies, you’re gonna
regret the day you ever met me.
‐Oh, rest assured, I will
not let her die so easily.
Now, will you become my servant?
Do so, and I shall
grant you a wish.
‐You go to hell.
Release me, that’s
all I want from you.
‐Then I’m taking the
girl along with me.
‐No!
Put her down!
Where are you taking her?
‐Come to my dream castle.
That is, if you so desire.
You can’t escape me for long.
Dammit!
Shippo, where’s this
dream castle of hers?
‐Wh‐‐what are you asking me for?
How should I know?
‐Wait.
There’s a saying a priest
once told my family.
Perhaps it can help
us find the castle.
The castle of the heavenly being
lies in the lake of Motosu,
unreachable by mortals.
‐So tell me, Hachi, why do you
think my grandfather didn’t
use his wind tunnel
on this Kaguya?
‐Oh, come on, isn’t it obvious?
Your grandfather
destroy a woman?
This celestial maiden was
probably a real beauty.
‐You don’t say?
I’m quite looking
forward to meeting her.
‐You never change.
Always on the prowl.
[laughter]
‐Whoa, is this the
cave of the shrine?
‐Hush.
Someone has arrived ahead of us.
‐Huh?
‐Don’t move a muscle.
Please, hang on, Sango!
‐Is that you, Miroku?
What are you doing here?
‐Sango?
How I longed to see you!
‐Miroku, come on.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Let go!
Let go of me!
‐How my hands have
yearned for this.
[slap]
‐Ah, this pain brings
back fond memories.
It’s been far, far
too long, Sango.
‐Well, you haven’t changed
a bit, you pervert.
‐I know.
I know.
I’m glad you found
Kohaku safe and sound.
‐Yes.
Unfortunately, his
memory is still unclear.
‐It’s gone.
I don’t believe it.
e mirror, as well
as the jeweled sprig.
They’re both gone.
‐The swallow’s cowrie
shell is gone, as well.
Kagura came and
stole it from Kohaku.
MIROKU: This poses
a serious problem.
HACHI: Master Miroku, was
this cowrie thing also
necessary to break the spell?
‐It was.
The five treasures possessed
represent the five elements.
And those five elements are
wood, fire, earth, metal,
and water.
‐Ah‐‐ one of the five treasures
is the cost of the fire rat.
Do you think it could be the
same cloth that Inuyasha wears?
‐If so, we’ll meet up
with him soon enough.
‐A castle in the lake.
‐I can’t believe
the demonic aura.
‐Time and the full moon are
fully aligned once more.
An eternal dream, a
celebration this night.
And now, let it all begin.
‐Our fears are justified.
‐The demonic aura
is growing stronger.
‐She stops time without
care or remorse,
and destroys all living
things in her wake.
‐Huh?
‐There’s a glow
beyond the forest.
Are we going, Inuyasha?
‐I don’t know about you two,
but shouldn’t we avoid danger?
‐Well, if that’s how you feel,
then stay here out of the way,
OK?
‐Inuyasha!
Akitoki, this is bad!
Real bad!
If demons accost us
now, we’ll be done for!
‐Good point!
‐Damn there, Kilala.
Kilala!
‐Master, we’d better be careful.
‐Oh, no.
Hachi, watch out!
‐Miroku!
No!
[scream]
‐Hachi, are you all right?
Please, speak to me.
Hachi!
[snoring]
‐Kohaku, I want you
to hang on tight, OK?
‐Yes, Miss Sango.
‐Look.
There’s something in the water.
‐Sango!
‐Shippo!
‐Kagome!
‐Inuyasha!
‐So you’ve shown yourself.
INUYASHA: Kagome!
Are you all right?
‐Inu‐‐ Inuyasha?
Inuyasha!
‐The wound has healed.
Such is the power of
the celestial robe.
My wish shall be realized.
‐Kagome, I’m coming to save you!
Just hang on!
Don’t give up on me!
‐Inuyasha!
‐What the‐‐
[scream]
That’s a‐‐
‐I knew I shouldn’t have
come along with you.
‐Damn!
Wind Scar!
This is taking too long.
I’ll use my Backlash Wave
and destroy it with one blow.
I can’t use my
Backlash Wave when
they’re coming at me
from all over the place.
‐Now I possess limitless power.
‐The celestial robe doesn’t
suit a fake celestial
being such as you.
‐You wouldn’t attack one
of your own, would ya?
That blows that theory.
Damn!
Huh?
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): I get it.
They’re all connected
at the base.
If I can destroy that‐‐
‐Watch this!
Wind Scar!
[scream]
‐Who shot that arrow?
‐Inuyasha, the rest
I shall leave to you.
‐That’s one obstacle down.
KAGURA: What?
Have you been conquered already?
How pitiful,
considering its size.
That act of yours is starting
to wear just a little bit thin,
I have to say.
‐It’s an act?
She’s not a real
celestial being.
‐Kanna told me.
You’re just like Naraku.
You both consume the
flesh o other demons
to increase your own strength.
I’ll wager you even devoured
the real celestial maiden
to gain immortality.
‐Kagome!
KAGURA: I bet Naraku must have
wanted that body of yours.
‐I detest all these half demons.
‐Indeed, your hatred for
them must truly run deep.
Let me remind you, I am
a woman born of Naraku,
and I’m growing rather
tired of your antics.
‐You’ll confront me, then?
That should be entertaining.
‐How about I suck the
soul out of your body?
[laughter]
‐What’s the matter
with you, Kanna?
‐You pathetic fools.
It’s not as easy as you
think to take my soul.
Perhaps I should tell you why
I sought the celestial robe.
[chanting]
‐Power of the
Mirror of Stillness.
‐No!
I can’t move!
‐Do you think that these things
will really heal injuries?
‐Kagome’s medicine kit
contains many things
with strange powers.
‐On another note, our little
Shippo was unusually brave
today, wasn’t he?
I suppose he does carry his
weight from time to time.
‐Akitoki, make sure his
bandage is good and tight.
HOJO: Yes.
‐Hey!
It was meant as a compliment.
‐Didn’t sound like it to me.
Hey, Akitoki, put a
bandage on my knee.
‐Yes, sir.
‐Shippo, who is
this man, anyway?
‐I do believe I’ve met you
somewhere before, haven’t I?
‐I doubt it.
‐Ignore him.
He’s not worth an introduction.
Hey, what are you doing, Miroku?
‐Somehow I don’t feel
quite right without it.
I guess I don’t paint
well with my left hand.
KAGUYA: Ah, so he’s come.
‐Inuyasha!
‐He will not interfere.
INUYASHA: Kagome!
‐Now, you beings who exist
in the realm of time,
vanish into the
void of illusion.
‐Inuyasha, stay away!
[shout]
‐Power of the
Mirror of Stillness.
‐Inuyasha!
‐What’s happening?
‐It’s Kaguya’s power of
the Mirror of Stillness.
‐She’s making time stop.
‐It’s coming!
It’s coming!
Oh, no!
It’s all over!
Father!
I’ll be joining you
in heaven any minute.
Huh?
‐Nothing happened.
‐Hey, wait.
I don’t get it.
Akitoki and Hachi aren’t moving.
‐Hey, look.
‐Kagome’s first
aid kit is glowing.
‐Her possessions obviously hold
a special power of their own.
They must be able to
put up a time barrier.
[shouting]
‐Aw.
These things are
making my eyes sting.
SANGO: Don’t you think we might
have gone a little overboard?
MIROKU: Perhaps just a little.
[laughter]
‐Oh, my beautiful
everlasting night, no one
shall disrupt us again.
‐Yeah?
Well, it’s not over yet.
‐Inuyasha!
‐Why are you still able to move?
‐That’s the least
of your worries.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
That pendant.
And he said he didn’t want it.
‐Look out, witch.
Time for a little payback!
What?
[laughter]
KAGOME: Inuyasha!
‐Kagome!
‐Inuyasha!
Inuyasha!
Where’d you go?
[laughter]
‐That unsightly
half demon was never
truly here in the first place.
‐An illusion?
[laughter]
KAGUYA: This is the dream
of the Pentacle Mirror.
illusion, the dream
castle beyond the mirror.
KAGOME: Inuyasha!
‐You’re all right.
Where’s Kagome?
‐Kaguya took her
into the castle.
‐Where did the
castle disappear to?
‐Take a look.
‐What happened to your sleeve?
I’ve never seen you
dress like a slob before.
‐Why take it out on me?
‐Well, why not?
‐The castle’s under here.
‐Kohaku?
Kohaku!
‐Let’s go.
‐Kohaku.
‐Kay.
I’m just a little kid!
It ain’t fair!
Whoa!
Hey, wait for me!
Whoa.
Where is everyone?
Wait!
Don’t leave me!
KAGUYA: Such fools, pursuing
me inside the mirror.
‐Why would you wanna
stop time anyway?
What’s the big attraction?
‐It seems only humans
such as yourself
are enamored by the
passage of time.
‐I’d rather die than stay
in this hellish void.
‐Don’t worry.
You won’t be here for long,
for I intend to eat you.
You possess the sacred
powers of a priesthood
and can put up a
barrier against time.
Those powers shall be mine.
‐Kaguya!
‐Inuyasha.
You guys.
You’re all OK.
‐We are, thanks to
your medical supplies.
‐Half demon.
Are you prepared to
become my servant yet?
‐Don’t count on it.
My sword‐‐ the Tetsusaiga!
‐Don’t worry.
I’ll take care of her.
Justice be done!
[chanting]
‐Sango!
‐Iron Reaver Soul Stealer!
‐Inuyasha!
Inuyasha!
‐Fox Fire!
Uh, you can take
over now, Miroku.
‐Take a good look, Inuyasha.
Behold the dark spirit
that lurks in your heart.
‐What are you rambling on about?
‐This is the true form
you desire to achieve,
and I am going to
grant your wish.
[chanting]
[growling]
‐Inuyasha.
Inuyasha!
‐I am the ruler of the
realm of the night.
I possess the power of darkness.
I shall release your true
form from the mirror.
‐Inuyasha.
‐Inuyasha’s transforming
into a full demon.
‐Yes, I see, but somehow
it’s different from before.
‐No, don’t!
Don’t transform!
‐Look at Inuyasha in the mirror.
He seems to be transforming.
‐This is your true
nature, Inuyasha.
Be the full demon
you’ve longed to become.
Seal your human
blood in this mirror
and be true to your own wishes.
‐What’s going on now?
‐If he transforms
into his full demon,
then it’s all over for him.
He can never be a
half demon again.
‐You’re not serious, are you?
‐But I thought
that Inuyasha could
control the transformations
from happening.
‐This is the world of
the mirrors, remember?
Perhaps the dark
desires of the heart
are somehow stronger in here.
SHIPPO: Does that mean
he’s a ferocious beast?
MIROKU: Exactly.
‐If we break it, we
can stop the change.
‐Sister, no!
Sango!
‐Kilala.
SHIPPO: Kagome!
Don’t worry.
I’ll set you free.
‐Inuyasha, snap out of it.
You’re not going to
sell your soul to Kaguya
and forget about us.
‐Excellent.
Only by releasing
the power of darkness
can one realize true freedom.
‐Listen to me, Kagome.
Inuyasha is still unsure
of what he desires,
but we can’t get through to him.
Only you can stop him.
If there was ever a time I
wished I had my wind tunnel,
it would be now.
‐Inuyasha, don’t do it!
Please stop!
Shippo.
I’ve got an idea.
Get my sacred jewel shards.
‐Huh?
‐Get my jewel shards!
‐Right, I’ll do it!
I want you to throw
the whole bottle at me.
‐Here comes!
‐Inuyasha!
Inuyasha!
I’m begging you.
Please don’t change.
Inuyasha.
‐Try what you will.
Your efforts are in vain.
e human heart he possessed
is locked inside this mirror.
He will never be a
half demon again.
‐Kagome, get away from him!
You’ll be killed.
‐I love you as a
half demon, Inuyasha!
To be honest, I like you
just the way you are.
There’s nothing wrong with
staying just the way you are.
[wicked laughter]
‐Inuyasha!
Inuyasha!
I love you.
I love you as a half demon.
‐What’s the matter, Inuyasha?
Why the hesitation?
[chanting]
[growling]
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): How can
I stop his transformation?
‐Oh boy.
‐Kagome.
‐Free the best of carnage
that lives inside you.
And, once you are
a full demon, bring
me the flesh of that girl.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): Inuyasha,
you want to stay with me,
don’t you?
‐What’s happening?
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): Kagome.
‐Hm?
What are these things?
‐Inuyasha.
Are you gonna be OK now?
‐Kagome.
‐Huh?
‐Are you nuts?
I could’ve really hurt you.
I’ll stay a half demon for a
while longer, just for you.
‐Mm‐hm.
‐No.
Stop this, Miroku.
Don’t go getting any ideas.
I don’t like that
look in your eye.
‐Sango.
‐You fool.
How could you abandon
such a fine opportunity?
‐Sango, come into my arms.
‐Kohaku.
Are you all right?
‐Idiot.
‐A half demon bearing
his fangs at me?
You have tempted your fate.
‐Hm?
‐The robe of the fire
rat is whole again.
‐I’ve had just
about enough of you!
What?
So you’re no
different from Naraku.
‐That’ll make destroying
her even easier.
[groaning]
‐What’s the matter, Kohaku?
‐My shoulder feels
like it’s burning up.
SANGO: Huh?
It can’t be!
[groaning]
‐The wind tunnel.
‐Let me see.
Hurry, Miroku!
Seal it up right now!
‐Please, sister.
Get away from me.
‐Kohaku!
‐What’s happening to him?
Oh, no!
‐I don’t know,
but it’s not good.
‐Kohaku, I’m right here.
‐Sango‐‐
‐Don’t worry, I’ll
never leave you again.
[scream]
KAGOME: Sango!
‐Naraku.
‐It’s been far too long, Kaguya.
I thought you were dead.
‐Correct.
I was dead‐‐ just long
enough to lure you out.
‐I don’t believe
what I’m hearing.
You faked your death for a while
and removed my wind tunnel?
‐How cruel.
How could Naraku do this to you?
‐Inuyasha!
Naraku intends to absorb Kaguya.
‐No one will interfere.
‐Hang on.
I’ll cut you away from Naraku.
‐Run, Sango!
‐Let me go!
Don’t do this!
‐You have to get away, or
Naraku will absorb you, too!
‐Damn you.
Damn you to hell!
‐Don’t do it.
You’ll end up hurting Kohaku.
INUYASHA: I know that.
‐And now, become
one with my flesh.
‐Keep your vile
hands away from me.
[chanting]
‐Huh?
‐Kohaku!
‐Watch out!
[chanting]
INUYASHA: Where’s Naraku?
SHIPPO: Is he dead?
‐He’s not.
He’s still alive.
‐He’s gotta be hiding
in here somewhere.
‐Damn.
He’s watching us
from the shadows.
MIROKU: If we destroy Kaguya,
he’ll consume her body
and become immortal.
But if Kaguya wins,
she’ll destroy us.
In either case, Naraku benefits.
He was using us right
from the very beginning.
‐All right, I’ve heard
just about enough.
‐Inuyasha?
‐We’ll just kill them both
and solve the problem.
‐Yes.
I can use my wind tunnel
to my heart’s content.
‐Don’t even think
about interfering.
Kaguya is mine!
[shout]
‐You cannot defeat me so easily.
‐Listen, Shippo, transform
into a bow for me.
‐A bow?
But there’s no arrow.
KAGOME: Never mind.
Just do it!
‐You wench!
‐Oh, no!
[chanting]
‐Look!
The mirror’s glowing.
t’s the one that
sent Naraku flying.
‐Wind tunnel!
‐What are you thinking?
I told you to stay out of this.
‐I figured you’d say that.
SANGO: Kagome!
[chanting]
‐Another spell.
Inuyasha!
A direct attack won’t work!
‐Well, it’s too late.
‐Return to my darkness
and vanish forever.
‐Taste my Backlash Wave!
‐That pathetic trick won’t work.
‐It’s gone.
‐Inuyasha.
It’s coming!
‐Yeah, I know.
A frontal attack’s the only way.
‐All right, Shippo.
Ready for action?
‐Yeah!
‐Sorry.
‐Never mind.
Forget my pain
and just shoot it.
‐Wind Scar!
‐Is that the best you have
to offer me, half demon?
‐Go!
‐How was that?
KAGUYA: A mere half
demon, and a mortal.
‐We did it!
[shouting]
‐Hey Kagome, you need a lift?
‐Yes.
Thanks, Sango.
‐Good catch, Sango.
We’re fine over here.
‐Oh, what a headache.
‐What is that?
[laughter]
KAGUYA: My body
may be destroyed,
but I am heavenly being.
You, girl with
the sacred powers,
your body shall be mine.
‐No, Kagome!
‐Kagome!
[laughter]
‐Naraku!
‐Come, Kaguya.
‐Kagome.
Get down!
‐Inuyasha.
‐Wind Tunnel!
‐Are you all right, Kagome?
‐Kagome.
Kohaku.
‐We’d better hurry
and get out of here.
‐Yeah, but how?
Which way is out?
‐We’ll just follow Naraku.
That should get us back to land.
‐Wait, don’t leave me!
[wicked laughter]
‐Help.
Help!
She’s coming!
Inuyasha, you coward.
‐Huh?
Where’s Kaguya?
‐Don’t worry.
She’s gone.
We’re safe now.
‐Hey.
Look at that.
SHIPPO: The castle
is disappearing.
‐Look up there.
‐It’s all over.
‐No.
It’s not over quite yet.
Naraku is still alive,
let’s not forget.
‐That’s true.
But at least we were able to
destroy one thing he was after.
That’s something.
‐Hmph.
Just one isn’t enough.
HACHI: Master Miroku!
Over here!
‐Hachi!
[coughing]
SANGO: You’re both all right.
‐Ms. Kagome, look.
I have the celestial robe back.
‐And look.
Your staff, Master Miroku.
‐It’s amazing.
When I came to, the robe
suddenly fell from heaven.
‐Wow.
It found its way back
to its rightful owner.
Just like a puppy.
MIROKU: Sango.
‐Hm?
‐Before he disappeared, I
heard Kohaku call you sister.
It may be small, but it’s
something to be glad for.
‐Thanks for saying that, Miroku.
I think so too.
‐Grandfather.
Kaguya was indeed a beauty.
‐Such a fool.
‐You going somewhere
with this, Miroku?
‐No need to worry,
my dear Sango.
My heart belongs to you alone.
‐Idiot.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
The shooting star
granted at least
part of my wish.
Princess Kaguya of the ancient
legend returned to the moon.
Our journey, though,
is far from over.
SANGO: Kagome!
MIROKU: Kagome!
SHIPPO: Hurry up!
KAGOME: Wait up!
Why didn’t you tell
me you were going?
INUYASHA: Ah, you
wouldn’t have noticed.
You’re always too
busy daydreaming.
KAGOME: I don’t like
that tone, mister.
MIROKU: Now, now.
We destroyed Kaguya.
Let’s be happy and
count our blessings.
SANGO: Yes.
That’s enough
fighting for one day.
[music playing]
‐Ah.
This feels so good.
‐Oh, yes.
That’s right.
Sango.
We should follow suit.
‐Huh?
[slap]
MIROKU: Oi!
‐What do you think you’re doing?
‐What do you think?
Kagome and Inuyasha did it.
Why don’t we reap the
benefits of intimacy?
‐I don’t know what
you’re talking about.
I’m not listening.
La la la la.
t wasn’t like I
wanted to do it to you.
‐Hm?
‐Huh?
KAGOME: What exactly is
that supposed to mean?
UYASHA:it wasn’t my idea.
I mean, you’re the one
who forced yourself
on me, remember?
KAGOME: Inuyasha!
Sit!
SHIPPO: Inuyasha.
Grow up, would you?