Sorry.
I'm told visiting
hours are over.
I'm an executioner named Draht.
I serve Aura, the guillotine.
Don't fight.
I have come here to kill you.
I see.
Not pretending you
want peace anymore?
We've just begun.
I should warn you
that I am fairly strong.
Stronger than me?
Stronger even than
Aura the guillotine.
I doubt that very much.
Why?
For this fight is already over.
A magical wire, huh?
What an interesting spell.
You concentrated mana around
your neck to avoid decapitation.
You're level-headed.
which allowed you to keep your head when
an ordinary mage would have lost theirs.
Try what you will, but this wire is
among demonkind's strongest spells.
Humanity's feeble magic
doesn't stand a chance!
I shall saw through your mana
and the soft pink flesh underneath.
You're right.
I doubt there is anything I
can do to sever your thread.
Really?
That's all it took to
convince you you'd won?
Demons these days
are such a disgrace.
No experience
on the battlefield.
This mage... She took my arm!
You big child!
Let's talk this through!
That's one beast down.
If I report this attack to the Graf and exterminate the rest of
the town's parasites, a pardon is the least he could grant me.
This is going to
complicate things.
This food is delicious.
My master always said, you can tell if a
town is peaceful by how good the eats are.
Guess that goes
for this place too.
Mr. Stark.
No, order your own.
Let's talk to the Graf.
We can try to petition him
directly to release Mistress Frieren.
It's only a matter of time
until harm comes to this town.
If we can get her out of the
dungeon, she can defeat the demons.
That does feel
like our only option.
We don't stand a chance
against enemies like those.
Especially not the Lügner guy.
He seems dangerous.
He only looked at Frieren.
We were standing right there
next to him with the guards.
But his eyes were
locked on her alone.
He saw us as pawns that
he can knock out anytime.
My hands haven't
stopped shaking since.
You see?
One thought about him
and I'm spilling my drink.
Now it looks like I wet myself.
We have an important meeting.
Clean it up.
Graf Granat is with
Lügner and his men.
Maybe asking for a fight.
What wouldn't have stopped
the heroes should not stop us.
You're right.
If I lost my nerve here, I'd never
be able to face my master again.
Let's go!
You can hang on to that one.
Are you coming?
My body seems to think not.
I am no longer
detecting Draht's mana.
He must be dead.
What a fool.
He was careless.
Careless?
We are the right-hand men
of Lady Aura, her executioners.
You think mere
carelessness could kill us?
Just who exactly is that mage?
Apologies for
keeping you waiting.
It seems the mage I captured managed to
escape, and her guard was found beheaded.
A worrisome threat to peace.
We shall help you
with your search.
Linie is quite skilled at
detecting mine- No, we're fine.
Peculiar.
It appears that you are
missing one of your companions.
He'll be back soon.
He went to use the privy.
Without asking a
servant where it is.
My untrained eye can tell
that mage is of great skill.
Yet she allowed my men
to detain her without a fight.
She understands the
gravity of killing a guard.
Lord Lügner, I'll ask
you one last time.
Where is your other companion?
That idiot, Draht.
He has ruined everything.
Yet I find I can't complain.
For now it seems that violence is the
only way to resolve this predicament.
It would be a lie to say I'm
anything less than overjoyed.
Whatever you use to reason, be it words or swords,
the end result will ultimately be the same.
No matter your weapon
of choice, the weak will die.
Just like this sword's
former owner did.
Lügner!
You see?
We are but wild beasts.
But don't worry.
I won't kill you.
You're going to assist us in
removing this town's defensive barrier.
Shouldn't be too
much farther from here.
Excuse me.
That is you, isn't it?
Aren't you supposed
to be in jail?
Please don't tell me
that you broke out.
I didn't have a
choice in the matter.
A demon called Draht came
into my cell trying to execute me.
And though I took care of the issue, when demons
die they turn into monoparticles and vanish.
I don't understand
the connection.
Before visiting me, he killed
the man guarding the dungeon.
To better paint the scene, all to be found down
there was a guard beheaded by a magical wire.
And a lone mage.
So where might that put me?
You'll be sentenced to
death for killing the guard.
I think so too.
Which is why I have no
choice but to leave town.
Wait a moment.
If you leave, the remaining
demons will run wild.
Would you really
abandon these people?
Why don't you two
defeat them for me?
You make it sound
like an everyday chore.
We don't stand a chance in a
fight against monsters like them.
You're not going to fight them
just because they're strong?
Don't look so downcast.
I've fought more than my fair share of
demons, and you're no weaker than they are.
Okay, we'll fight them!
But you've gotta help us!
You can't ask us to go it alone!
We're begging you!
Hey, where do you
think you're going?
You can't leave
us to die, Frieren.
You don't know when to give up.
Steel your resolve, remember?
Steel yourself.
I don't wanna be demon food.
You're being childish.
About ten kilometers outside of
town, I sense a great deal of mana.
Someone is observing us.
Aura the Guillotine, one of the
Seven Sages of Destruction.
It isn't as if I enjoy facing
powerful enemies either.
All the more reason to
take care of this one swiftly.
This feels wrong.
You're sure we have to sneak in?
Well, I suppose we could just tell the gate
guards we're here to kill the peace envoys.
It's a little too quiet.
I truly love magic, you see.
Think of Qual, the
Elder Sage of Corruption.
His life revolved around magic.
That was the price for
developing his killing spell.
Such is the way of our kind.
We devote ourselves to research and spend our
lengthy lives studying a single type of magic.
We grow our knowledge
daily for years upon years.
Our magics might impress you now, but wait a decade and our
powers will be even greater, further cementing our strength.
Yet, magic is a strange thing.
This town's defensive barrier, created by Flamme the
Legendary Mage, has successfully kept demons out.
A spell cast by a genius a thousand years ago can
sometimes outmatch the research of the present.
I despise geniuses.
The beauty of accumulated
effort is lost on them.
Your family knows about
this barrier better than any.
You've maintained
it for generations.
You showed your hand when you
allowed our demonic presence into town.
Now I know Flamme's
creation can be controlled.
You will teach me how.
Perhaps you need
a moment to think.
I will leave you for now.
Making someone wait is a diplomatic
tactic we demons can employ as well.
If you refuse to speak with me,
know that further torture awaits.
There must be a grimoire related
to the barrier hidden somewhere.
Search his room.
I shall search the study.
It's you.
That snot-nosed adventurer kid.
I thought my son had
come to take me away.
You look awful.
Those demons are no joke.
Let me help you out.
Your hands are trembling.
Is that a problem?
No.
It is valiant.
My son's hands trembled
before he marched into battle, too.
Must've cast a
spell on the rope.
It won't cut.
Just leave me be.
I'm already done for.
Evacuate the townsfolk
while you still can.
You don't know your people if you think
they'd listen to a snot-nosed adventure kid.
The Granat family crest
hangs from my neck.
Show it to the guards and
they'll do whatever you say.
And watch your tone with me.
The way that you've spoken
thus far is a serious offense.
Although, I could
overlook your crime.
If you run now.
I get it.
Sorry, old-timer.
You better kiss your
fancy chair goodbye.
No chance I can
afford to replace him!
Lord Lugnia, it's a rat.
Graf Granat, do you know him?
I don't.
He's one of the
travelers passing through.
He must have come to ask me to free that
mage without realizing she's already escaped.
He's just a stupid boy.
I see.
Again...
You can be on your way.
I will let you live.
It's like before.
He's not even looking at me.
Step aside while you still can.
Get in my way and I'll kill you.
I'd like to see you try.
My... Fast.
For a human, that is.
You protected your vitals,
and your reflexes aren't bad.
That said, the young are rash,
whether they're human or demon.
Reckless with no strategy.
Though I have to admit, I do commend
your valor for challenging me on your own.
On my own?
Perfect.
If you can't feel her, I guess
her strategy was a good one.
Come again?
Well, Fern, I created the
opening like you told me to.
Lord Lügner!
I'm sensing a mage.
Impossible.
That mage is a mere human.
She was able to evade
Linie's mana detection.
And beyond that, this spell...
Sit back, my lord.
Let me handle this.
Don't.
Tell me, girl.
What is that spell?
Truly, it's nothing special.
It's just ordinary
offensive magic.
Solltrag in your magic system.
You expect me to
believe that was Solltrag?
Don't be absurd, child.
Demonkind overcame that spell half a century
ago, long before you walked this world.
From whom did
you learn this magic?
You're trying to
buy yourself time.
I'll end this.
You will not.
Fern, his injuries are bad.
There's no time for them.
Let's retreat.
Fine.
Once I stop the bleeding they're
through, I ask you take the warrior.
Those children have
been stained with my blood.
We will not lose them.
You needn't fight her
yourself, Lord Lügner.
I can kill the mage as well.
If it were you who'd been struck
by that spell, you'd be dead.
Already, Mighty, it's been modified from its
base form to specialize in killing demons.
In its current state, it's no
longer Solltrag, Killer of Man.
It has become a
demon-killing spell.
The way that girl moved reminded
me of a mage I faced before.
The same mage who first
struck me with that magic.
Of course, I remember now.
It was Frieren.
The mage who made great contributions to humanity's analysis of
Solltrag and sent more demons to the grave than anyone else in history.
Frieren the Slayer.
One of the geniuses I despise.