Frieren, you must go to
Aureole and speak with Himmel.
On the very northernmost end of the continent, I arrived
at the place the people of this world call Heaven.
I now know it as Aureole,
the land where souls rest.
Many spirits have
gathered there.
I spoke with friends whom
I once fought alongside.
Forgive me.
You have a long journey ahead.
It took the four
of us ten years.
I see.
So we'll be following the same route you took to
the Demon King's castle on your first journey.
That we will.
Another brief
ten-year adventure.
One one-hundredth, eh?
Frieren, you won't be
staying in the Royal Capital?
I'm going to keep traveling.
All by yourself?
It's easier that way.
You're not going to
take on an apprentice.
A journey is better
with someone to talk to.
I fear it would be
a waste of time.
No matter how much I
teach them, they'll surely die.
How cheery.
That's not how
relationships work.
That's how they work for me.
Just consider our adventure.
It's taken up less than one
one-hundredth of my life.
Sounds like me, I suppose.
It's funny, don't you think?
What is?
How much that one
one-hundredth has changed you.
Goodbye for now.
For now.
In comparison, for me,
our journey's been one half.
I've spent one half
of my life with you.
It's going to be much
more than that from here on.
It's a story of love, a sign of the end, a
journey that goes on forever, it's up to you.
It's a memory of a short journey with a hero who
defeated evil that once cast a shadow on this land.
Reiwa mushou ni hito wo wasure saseru Soko ni ikita kiseki mo sabitsuiteku Soredemo
kimi no kotoba mo negai mo yuuki mo Ima wa tashikani watashi no naka de ikiteru
Oh my god!
Take these words to heart, Fern.
Before long, Frieren will
be the one in charge of you.
Listen to her and
be a good girl.
If you don't...
If I don't what?
I'll come back as a
ghost and haunt you.
So just to make certain, you're saying that if I'm
a bad girl, you'll pay me a visit after you're gone?
You've grown into
quite the sly young lady.
Wherever did you pick that up?
I take it back.
If you're on your best behavior, then I might be
willing to stop by and say hello every now and again.
We should be arriving
at the village soon.
That was fast.
What's that?
Nothing very important.
Greetings, adventurers.
Heading to the mountain pass?
I wouldn't if I were you.
Several people have
gone missing there recently.
Killed by monsters?
They were taken by ghosts,
according to all of the rumors.
Folks have seen them
with their own eyes.
Could be the undead.
Do you know what
these ghosts look like?
I've been too scared to ask.
But if you're that curious, there
are plenty who could tell you.
Here's what we've learned.
The ghosts take on the form of the
Beholder's dead family member or friend.
They look just
as they did in life.
A couple of witnesses even
claim that the ghosts spoke to them.
We can conclude this
isn't the work of the undead.
How are you so sure?
The undead are merely
corpses being controlled by magic.
Things like zombies
and skeletons.
But our specters are reported
to appear as they did in life.
A reanimated corpse
couldn't do that.
All that to say, we're dealing with
another type of monster entirely.
Seems you know what
monster that might be.
Yes, a nasty one.
We'd best be
careful to avoid it.
We'll take our leave
first thing in the morning.
But Mistress Frieren, it's clear
the villagers need our help.
You're starting to sound just
like Himmel and the others.
The biggest difference between
you and me is that I am a good girl.
All right.
If you want to
help them, we shall.
We'll be traveling through
the mountain pass either way.
The missing villagers
didn't vanish into thin air.
Plenty of clues.
A generous monster.
There are signs of
magic usage all around us.
Yes, indeed.
Can you tell what type it was?
Illusion magic.
In my book on magical
ecology, there's this creature.
It uses lifelike illusions
to lure in its prey.
The Einzahm.
It preys exclusively upon people, using craftiness
rather than strength to lure in its unsuspecting meals.
It tricks its victims with
phantoms of the dead.
And they really fall for that?
Who wouldn't want a final
moment with their dearly departed?
Thankfully for the two of us, the Einzahms' illusions aren't
a threat to mages who know to look beyond their tricks.
They're easily dispersed
by high-density mana.
Basic offensive magic should do.
So all I have to do is
shoot through the phantoms.
Could you?
Yes, of course.
Especially now that
I know they're fake.
I once had to shoot an illusion
of my master begging for her life.
Though to be fair, her begging
not to die was a regular occurrence.
So I can't say that I
felt particularly guilty.
Regardless, it
certainly isn't fun.
Why were you accustomed
to hearing her beg for her life?
The mist is growing thicker.
We're not far.
If you see a specter,
don't hesitate to shoot.
Fern.
There it is.
A phantom of the dead.
No problem.
Just shoot.
Look at that, mage.
You've surpassed my
wildest dreams, my dear.
I decided to come
back and say hello.
A girl as good as you are
deserves a friendly haunting.
It knows.
The path of the mage called
and you wisely followed.
Since you were a child, your love
for magic... My cherished memories.
It knows all of them.
And it's using them against me.
How cruel.
Need help?
Seems you might.
I didn't expect to see Himmel.
I was sure it would show me my
master like the last one I defeated did.
Perhaps this means I've changed
since I last encountered one.
Frieren, shoot.
Impressive.
That's just what he'd say.
And now the mountain
pass is safe once more.
That thing I just saw... That was
only a phantom of Master Heiter.
A shadow.
Correct.
It's high time we
go see the real thing.
If there's anywhere we might
find him, it would be Aureole.
You're right.
That's a dragon?!
I've never seen
one in real life.
Look at its nest.
Do you see that grimoire?
I've been after that
one for a long time.
That doesn't surprise me.
Why is it there of all places?
Dragons are known to seek out objects
infused with magic to build their nests.
That's a solar dragon.
No doubt it has dined
on many an adventurer.
Grimoire or otherwise, we
should eliminate the beast.
Be careful not to
destroy the nest.
Right.
So, uh, that didn't do anything.
They are very
resilient creatures.
No choice, then.
Run!
Finally lost it.
This one's a fast flyer.
No aerial battle for us.
I thought...
I thought I was
gonna die right there.
Let's head back that way.
If we continue to wear it down,
the brute will eventually give in.
Good point.
Playing tag with dragons is not
within a mage's job description.
Uh...
We'll have to take on
another companion.
A frontliner?
Yes.
You're searching
for one, aren't you?
In a village near Regal Canyon,
you'll find a warrior named Stark.
Pick him up on your way
into the Northern Lands.
He's my apprentice.
Right.
Is he any good?
Hard to think there's
a dragon here.
It's so peaceful.
'Tis indeed.
I've been meaning to ask, what sort of
spell does that grimoire contain anyway?
One that lets you
see through clothes.
You really do gather only the
strangest of spells, Mistress Frieren.
That is my hobby.
But this one is practical, too.
Depending on what the user views as clothing,
it could reveal hidden weaponry or...
Travelers, may I have
a moment of your time?
Mr. Stark would like
to meet the two of you.
That saves us a
fair bit of trouble.
It was three years back now.
The dragon attacked,
nearly destroying the village.
That's when he appeared.
The brave Mr. Stark.
The dragon was fierce, but
our brave hero didn't break.
After a long standoff,
the monster flew away.
It was a sight to behold.
Since that day, he has lived alongside us in the village, and
that dragon has been too scared to rear its ugly head ever again.
Three whole years of peace.
Perfect.
He sounds like just
the person we need.
The dragon's done for.
I hope you're right.
Do you think I can be a
strong warrior like you?
Sure you can.
But being a warrior's
rougher than it looks.
It's Grandma!
So you're the ones who've
been messing with the dragon.
Don't get that
thing too worked up.
You'll put the whole
village in danger.
Dragons are serious.
They're not the fairy tale
creatures you think they are.
One of them gave me this scar.
I was fighting a shadow dragon and-
That's child's play as far as injuries go.
My master put you
up to this, didn't he?
Who are you?
I am known as Frieren the Mage.
Hey, Gran, mind
giving us some privacy?
It's alright.
They're acquaintances
of my master.
Don't hold back.
He must be furious.
I left without so
much as a word.
Stark, you have no reason
to remain in this village.
Why haven't you
defeated the dragon?
Tell me what you want and
maybe I'll think about sharing.
If you're here to send me back to
my master, you can forget about it.
We're in need of a warrior
and would like for you to join us.
Though before that, we would appreciate
your help in defeating the dragon.
I want the Grimoire in its nest.
Why's that?
It's a hobby.
No particular reason.
We're dealing
with a solar dragon.
You don't fight it
without a good reason.
That's amazing!
You're right.
Mine is that a fool once praised
me for the spells I collected.
Is that enough of a reason?
For a little praise?
That's ridiculous.
Agreed.
I don't mind joining your party.
I can tell my master
put you up to this.
But no matter.
My priority is taking
out the Solar Dragon.
I've had difficulties
defeating it on my own.
For you, it'd be
no issue, right?
No, not at all if you can keep
the beast busy for 30 seconds.
Loud and clear.
Just 30 seconds, huh?
and that really
has to be my job.
Is there some kind of
joke that I'm missing here?
I can't say that
I'm very surprised.
Tell me, Stark, just how many
monsters have you fought?
A big fat zero, okay?
Don't abandon me,
Frieren, I need your help.
I worked up the guts to confront the dragon,
but I was so terrified I couldn't move a muscle.
I mean, come on.
That thing slices through
houses like they're veggies.
The human being doesn't
stand a chance against it!
I figured that it spared me on a whim, but…
The dragon stopped attacking the village
after that and I was treated like a hero!
The villagers are too
nice for their own good!
A strong young man
like you should eat up!
Stark!
After supper, you gotta
show me all your latest moves!
There's no way I could leave
this place even if I wanted to!
This one's no good.
We should get going
and find someone serious.
Please don't leave
me here to rot!
No, he can hold off the dragon.
I'm certain of it.
Fine, but it'll take more
than a pat on the back.
Well, Stark, you have
till tomorrow morning.
Think it all through.
You know as well as I do
you can't keep the hero act up.
I heard you met Mr. Stark.
A fine young man, isn't he?
He's just lovely.
When we cook for him, it seems his
stomach is almost as big as his smile.
Everyone really
seems to love that guy.
I'm sure that they do.
He struck me as a
kind sort of person.
Maybe so.
I was distracted by
his immense cowardice.
The lad is a little
yellow-bellied.
But let's think back to your first
time going up against a monster.
Never mind.
Let's think forward.
You were cute once.
Not only are you taller than
me now, but scarier, too.
What I want to know is why
the dragon hasn't been attacking.
Who can say?
It might be bored of
this place, or perhaps...
What was that sound?
Stark, I imagine.
If you're curious, you
should go check on him.
I'm going to bed.
Right.
Is he any good?
When his village was attacked by
monsters, he fled and never looked back.
He's a coward who
left his home to burn.
He's like me.
That's why I hammered
everything I know into the boy.
Now he's finally ready to fight
for someone other than himself.
You've sold me.
He is any good.
I see now.
Your training is what
made this fissure.