You three seem close, so how long
have you been traveling together?
My travels with Mistress Frieren began
four years ago, but I've known her longer.
It's been about a year for me.
Makes sense.
You know, there's still
something this party lacks.
What?
Wanna take a guess?
Let's see... We've got our front liner, a
decent priest, and a near surplus of mages.
Could you mean a thief?
Someone to out-swindle the
mimic she's always falling for?
When it comes to treasure chests,
the reward always outweighs the risk.
No.
What we lack is something even more vital.
And that's a nice-looking older lady!
Most parties won't even leave
town until they've found a broad!
That's the way, or else
you're vixenless like us!
Is that right?
Come on, don't forget about Frieren.
She's more of an elderly child than a lady.
He looks so distraught.
My apologies.
Hey!
You can finally see the next village!
They're still breathing.
Yeah, same here.
What's the deal with this place?
Why'd they all fall asleep?
I say we move along to the next village.
This smells like trouble.
Even for you, that's cold.
I was only teasing.
A curse, no doubt.
I thought as much.
What a headache.
This may sound dumb,
but what even is a curse?
Among the spells utilized by monsters and demons are
those that put people to sleep or turn them into stone.
Those whose mysteries humankind is yet to unravel are
what we call curses, a placeholder for the unknown.
Humanity's magic can't explain the
principles behind them or how to lift them.
Does that mean it's already
too late to save these people?
It is only the magic of man
that faces such an impasse.
The magic of the goddess that
priests use is a different story.
Dispelling curses has long
been the business of the clergy.
Well, Sein, suppose you can help them?
Don't rush me.
I need to determine the
type and source of this thing.
I thought magic was magic.
What makes the goddesses so unique?
The magic of the goddess is
recorded in holy scriptures, you see.
Only those who own them can wield it.
Much like the demon's magic, the principles
behind the bulk of it aren't understood.
So it's not the sort of
thing that holds my interest.
That, and it's incredibly difficult to use
unless you're born with a certain knack.
That same predisposition comes
with an increased resistance to curses.
It's what the faithful bunch
call the blessing of the goddess.
And it's the reason this sleepy
spell won't affect our priest.
So not even a mage at your level
can really defend against curses?
We mages can't detect them,
let alone defend against them.
Though I do feel that I am
under attack for some reason.
So I can conclude that this place
is still under the power of the curse.
My soul feels itchy.
You can't just say scary things like that and
expect me not to turn into a giant sniveling baby!
This isn't a low-grade everyday
spell we're dealing with here.
Can you lift it or can't you?
I would need the right tools.
Honestly, it might be easier to take
out the source than to treat its symptoms.
It's coming from a monster,
and I know where it is.
Let's go.
I like how you cut to the chase.
Mistress Frieren.
It's Mr. Stark.
That didn't take long.
Any chance you can temporarily wake him?
I told you I don't have the proper tools.
As is, I could only keep
him up for five seconds.
That's practically nothing.
In any case, looks like we should hurry.
Fern's out cold, too.
So much for her taking a little break.
We've lost half of our manpower.
Our odds are starting to look grim.
I put up a barrier.
We'll hide them here for now.
We're almost there.
I can sense it.
Good.
Say, Sein, wake me when
the monster shows up.
I don't want you fighting
that creature alone.
I promise you now that I shall defeat it.
Were you not listening?
I can only give you... Frieren?
You can't defeat it in five seconds.
So be it.
I have battle magic too.
It's a subspecies of chaos flower.
It must be feeding off
the sleeping villagers.
It'll sap their mana
away until it kills them.
Chaos flowers are known to merge with the
local flora and branch off into new variations.
Almost mirror-like.
Though they come in different shapes and sizes,
they all have the same weak spot at their core.
Three Spears of the Goddess!
What was that about?
I didn't think the blasted
thing would reflect my magic.
Unless I land a direct hit on the core, the leaves
can deflect whatever I throw at it in any direction.
If I'm not careful, it could hit Frieren.
Damn it!
This can only get worse from here.
Should I heed the elf's
orders and wake her?
She's the mage from the Party of Heroes.
If a spell of hers were deflected, it would destroy
not only the forest, but the entire village with it.
I'd only have five seconds.
That's not enough time to explain.
As sharp as Frieren is, we haven't had time to develop
any kind of shared trust or mutual understanding.
I can't even get a read on her.
What goes on in that ancient head?
That's right.
You might find it hard to believe,
but I can never tell what she's thinking.
Shared trust is a luxury.
As in, it's not something adventurers need.
Nothing has to be unspoken.
I know this because my companion Frieren was
terrible at cultivating mutual understanding.
Since intent couldn't be assured with a look
or a touch, I decided I would trust her words.
For example, she swore to us all
that she would defeat the Demon King.
Though it was a bold
claim, I chose to believe her.
Trust her words, huh?
I don't want you fighting
that creature on your own.
I promise you now that I shall defeat it.
That face didn't look
ready to defeat anything.
Whatever happens, don't blame me!
A Wickeding Spell!
Frieren!
Only the core!
Done.
Simple enough.
Thank you very much.
I won't forget what you've done for us.
It's nothing.
I can assure you we didn't do much, ma'am.
Hush now.
I've never been happier
to have my sleep disturbed.
I knew our flower was
the type that reflects magic.
I recognized it the moment you woke me up.
There's no question that
you're an incredible mage.
That might be the case, but you're
the reason we made it out of there alive.
Thank you very much, Sein.
That lady from the village sure was pretty.
You're still on that?
So that's Foresh, huh?
More importantly, it's the
midpoint in our journey to Oyserst.
We're only halfway there?
This really is a long journey.
While we're here, let's drop
in and replenish our supplies.
Um, Mistress Frieren?
I hate to be the bearer of bad
news, but our funds are-Hey!
You there.
What now?
That looks like a noble's carriage.
Huh?
Excuse you!
What is going on?!
He has a good physique.
His looks aren't bad either.
Get in.
I'll take you to my mansion.
Does anybody care to explain?!
Who are you, lad?
The name is Stark.
Lord Ordon, sir.
You cannot hold us without reason.
I need no introduction, I see.
This mansion is home to the Ordens, one of the
three great families of the Northern Lands.
Your grandfather, he was pushy too.
I don't know what nonsense you're trying to
engage me in, but I'm preoccupied at the moment.
Stark and I need to have a word.
If you can talk to my
warrior, you can talk to me.
Tell me, Stark.
Do you need your mommy's
permission to have a conversation?
Come on, don't fight.
I have a job for you,
and I will pay you well.
No, no chance.
We're leaving, Stark.
Mistress Frieren.
What's with the copper?
That's the remainder of our funds.
I suppose that at the very
least we can hear you out.
Akimi.
So, Stark, from where do you hail?
I'm from a warrior village
in the Klee region, sir.
I know the place.
My family line originates
from the very same region.
My eldest son, Wirt.
He is a hero of this city,
and the heir to my title.
He looks like you, Mr. Stark.
Indeed he does.
If we changed you and cleaned you up, only a
close family member could discern the difference.
I have a feeling that's going
to play into your job offer.
About a month ago now, we took a
vast army of demons on head-to-head.
My son lost his life on the battlefield.
He and the enemy
commander killed each other.
The only silver lining, if you could call it as
much, is that it happened in a large-scale melee.
Very few know he's dead.
Gabel is aware, as well as
some of my most trusted men.
So what is it that you're
planning to make Stark do?
Voresh is a powerful fortress city,
a key player in this region's defense.
Until we can rebuild the forces we
lost, we can't allow morale to slip.
So you want to cover up
your son's death until then.
Three months from now, all of the area's most
influential figures will gather at a soiree.
We'll show them there
that Wirt is alive and well.
And our reward?
I will give you ten Strahl gold coins.
That would be three meals a
day for an entire year, plus snacks.
Sweeten it with a grimoire.
You can have your pick of the
library after our work is done.
One problem.
I'm not your guy.
Folks aren't gonna miss
the big scar on my forehead.
The people believe Wirt is currently
recovering from damage taken in combat.
That's an honorable battle scar.
Mr. Stark, we need the money.
More pathetic.
Gabel, I leave the boys'
etiquette training to you.
Mr. Stark, how is etiquette
training coming along?
It's slowly killing me.
What do you think?
Doesn't suit you.
Typical.
Well, my lady, I must get some air.
Lord Ordon.
Haven't I told you a hundred
times to call me father?
You never know whose
prying eyes could be upon us.
Aren't you being a little bit cold?
It's only been two months since
your actual son passed away.
All that I've done has been in
accordance with my son's final wishes.
I even had another double prepared.
He didn't look as much
like him as you do, though.
Trust me, it's not as if I
enjoy this cruel charade.
But it's what my son wanted.
So cooperate, would you?
You're not too big on
the people skills, huh?
Stand tall.
Don't shrink yourself, Mut.
Yes, father, of course.
That's my second son, Mut.
Despite the fact he's to be my heir
now, he shows little improvement.
Then, of course, there's your brother.
Our family's great shame.
Having skill with a sword
affects one's posture.
I shall teach you the
technique of the Orden family.
What's wrong?
It's all right.
Take deep breaths.
This isn't your village.
You're safe to learn here.
I realize he's still a kid, but
what do you think of Moot?
He doesn't have his brother's talent.
But he's a hard worker.
Time and effort are
investments that always pay off.
Once he's grown, he'll be a far
stronger knight than I ever was.
Gotcha.
You should really tell
that to Moot instead of me.
I tell him all the time.
Now it's gone to his head
and he refuses to get better.
That's a whole different kind of problem.
Huh?
You're saying I have to learn
all that etiquette stuff too?
Well, it is a soiree.
Do you really expect a man of his age
to attend such a function on his own?
I suppose his mommy could
always escort him instead.
Good luck, Fern.
This past month has been
nothing short of torture.
But anything for the money, right?
I'm sorry about all that.
We've been practicing this for ages.
We might as well.
It still doesn't suit you, you know.
Would you like to dance as well?
I'd like to eat.
Fair enough.
If not for this damn injury, I would
have been in the vanguard alongside him.
Perhaps then Wirt would still be with us.
M'lord.
It looks like the soiree's wrapping up.
You've completed your work with us.
Gabel, see to it Frieren gets her reward.
I've found you're far more powerful a
warrior than you appear at first glance.
If you ever need a place to stay
I'm sorry, sir, but I can't replace your son.
Of course you can't.
No more than I could
ever replace your father.
But you don't have a home to return to.
The warrior village of the Klee
region was destroyed by demons.
I'm certain of that much.
My son and I parted ways in anger.
All due to some petty argument.
I worked myself into a fit of rage and told
him I never wanted to see his face again.
I didn't mean one bit of it.
When I first came upon you,
I mistook you for a miracle.
That's all the more
reason I can't stay here.
I said things I didn't mean and parted in
anger, too, with the man who raised me.
So now, my hope is to make things right
by bringing him back stories of my travels.
I wish you well.
Hmm... Should I rule out
Grimoire Y or Grimoire Z?
Mistress Frieren, you've
been deciding for half a day.
You're distressing Mr. Gobel.
Please hurry.
Look, you trained the
poor man's life force.
They say it'll still be some time before
their troops are back to what they were.
What's up?
Nothing.
At the very least, he won't
have to worry about his heir.
Forgotten heroes, huh?
They're forgotten heroes.
More like degraded.
No one knows their names.
Humans develop quickly.
He's a long-lived friend of mine.