Though so.
I know an adventurer when I see one.
A thrilling profession you’ve got
I once hoped to join your ranks.
I guess that’s what kids do.
Dream big foolish dreams that always fall flat.
When I was younger, I
played sidekick to a friend
who used to go on all
sorts of little adventures.
Foolhardy and with energy to spare, he was
like a gorilla trapped in the body of a kid.
That said, he was a good kid
who always cared for his friends.
As we grew up, I forgot our
dreams of braving the unknown.
Until he invited me to join his
party and become the real thing.
I wonder how different my life would
be if I'd only taken his hand back then.
It's been ten years now since that
happened, and I regret it to this day.
And why exactly are
you sharing this with me?
Well, my village's harvest
festival is coming up.
My brother sent me into the woods to find some
herbs for cooking, which should have been no issue.
But you see...
I fell in a bottomless
swamp and it became one.
Hear me out.
My biggest regret was not taking his hand.
So please, don't let
yours be not taking mine.
You have a chance to change my fate here.
Just give me a moment.
I need to think.
Huh?
You're messing with me.
What's so confusing it
requires that much thought?
Your hand is dirty.
I'm gonna drown in this muck.
You can wash your
hands off later, can't you?
And besides, miss,
To a certain extent.
We grown-ups are dirty by nature.
Please.
I've met countless adults,
but none quite as filthy as you.
I must ask you for more time.
If you would let me think, I
might recall this belt to pull you out.
Got it.
But could we pick up the pace a bit?
Let me see...
Mistress Frieren, did you
have any luck finding herbs?
Oh, I remember.
I can take it from here, thanks.
You're so welcome.
Sorry for the trouble my mistress caused.
Hey, I'm in no spot to complain.
Your friend there saved my life.
Perhaps, but regardless,
I will scold her later.
My night off.
Are you folks sure you don't need
to stop by the village before you go?
We're busy preparing for the festival, but
I'd like to find some way to say thanks.
We're hoping to reach a larger town today.
Our supplies are low, so we
need a good place to restock.
Understood.
Well, in that case, be careful.
There are a lot of dangerous, venomous
creatures out there in those woods.
Good to know.
Hey, something just bit me.
What?
You have to be kidding.
We were told to be on the lookout for
that sort of danger mere moments ago.
First things first, let's
bandage the wound.
My nose might be bleeding a little.
Any spell that has to do with identifying poison
falls into a priest's realm, so I'm no help.
I don't recognize this reaction, so the
antidotes we have might not do the job.
We should get you checked
at a church to be safe.
Now, Fern, for how much longer
can you use your flying magic?
I would say we only have about 30
minutes, since it consumes a lot of mana.
Unfortunately, that won't
get us all the way to the town.
We'll have to head back to that village.
Leave moving the patient to me.
It's really not that big a deal.
I'm going to be fine, trust me.
My master taught me that the best way
to beat poisons is to just tough them out.
Come to think of it, I have seen Eisen take several
poison-coated arrows to the back and be fine.
It was enough to knock out a dragon.
Heiter was appalled.
You get it?
No.
The only thing that tale proves is
Mr. Eisen is very far from normal.
What's more, Master Heiter would always remind me,
poison's the cause of 20% of adventurer deaths.
We should hurry.
Why?
This is complete overkill.
I'm afraid you're too late.
A few hours from now,
his brain will start to melt.
At that point, it will flow from his nose.
And then he'll die!
That's terrifying!
Please guide us, Father.
There must be something we can do for him.
That bite was deadly, and could typically
only be cured if treated immediately.
But perhaps my brother
will be able to help you.
There you are.
We have a problem, brother.
We both agree this new
tub is too small, right?
There's honor in poverty.
Sure, to a point, maybe.
But impoverishing down to a
tub fit for fingertips seems extreme.
We have greater concerns.
Take a look at this boy for me, Sein.
Hold on.
These are the adventurers
I was telling you about.
They're the folks who rescued me.
Look at you.
You were bitten by a snake, huh?
Glad you took my warning to heart.
There.
Consider my debt repaid.
So long.
I'm going to help out at the plaza.
All right.
I'm not bleeding.
And there's no brains.
Seems the effects of the poison are gone.
Tell me, Father, is he...
He's my little brother,
and quite the priest.
That holy symbol around
your neck, it's awarded to the
most outstanding priest in
a region by the Holy Capital.
Your brother came in and instantly cured a poison
a top-level healing expert called Incurable.
He's no less than a genius.
I had a feeling you of all people
would notice, Miss Frieren.
I didn't realize you knew who I was.
Mr. Heiter told me many a story about you.
He's who gave me this.
He came from the capital to observe us, and
I suppose he thought I was doing rather well.
However, I'm still just a
provincial priest in a small village.
This medallion is my greatest achievement.
And while I'm very proud, the truth is,
my ability doesn't even compare to Sein's.
You see, we lost our parents.
He was just a child when it happened.
Though I was young myself when
they passed away, I raised my brother.
When he was little, he would often talk
about becoming an adventurer someday.
He didn't want to grow up to be an
ordinary village priest because he
couldn't bear for all his days to
look the same, the way that mine do.
He would tell me that with
eyes full of hopes and dreams.
That shine has dimmed now, as he
becomes more like me each passing year.
His soul is aching for something greater.
So please, take my brother with you on
your journey and away from this village.
It's perfect.
You clearly need a priest.
And I'm certain he needs
someone to give him that final push.
Come on, Frieren.
He's an easy yes.
The man's a genius.
What is there to think about?
Whatever it is, it can't be worth risking
my brains coming out of my nose again.
He would make things safer, and our journey's
headed deeper into the unknown from here.
Why are you acting so
wary, Mistress Frieren?
An aversion to my own kind, I suppose.
Yeah, I don't know what
that's supposed to mean.
I don't care.
I'm inviting him whether you like it or not.
Where's he going?
Maybe the bar downstairs?
I get the feeling Mr. Sein
spends a lot of time there.
Of course.
Alcohol.
Tobacco.
Gambling.
So, at what point does
Corrupt become Depraved?
I'm just getting to know my fellow man.
Care to join us, kid?
The name is Stark.
And I came to ask you to join us.
We are looking for a priest.
That's a funny joke.
But I'm already a priest for the village.
I can't go adventuring.
Wait, this could be fun.
Take a load off, Stark.
If you can beat me at a
hand, I'll join your party.
Are you for real?
Man of the cloth and my word.
Please don't do it!
Miss Frieren, I think I just heard
Mr. Stark yell from downstairs.
It looks like someone robbed him blind.
How awful.
Who would do such a thing?
No hard feelings.
We grown-ups are dirty,
and we play dirty, too.
Someone's robbed him blind, too.
That someone would be the village chief.
A tyrant's got lady luck on a leech.
Sein.
I hear that you're looking for a priest.
Look elsewhere.
You want to become
an adventurer, don't you?
There's a massive difference
between want and wanted.
It's too late for me now.
See, I should have left when there was
a chance I could have actually found him.
And if that's not enough, now I
don't even have the wardrobe for it.
Frieren, defeat the Demon King.
Join our party.
It's too late for me.
It's been over 500 years now
since I last fought a demon.
Their battles I've long
forgotten how to win.
I deferred that decision
for centuries too long.
I missed the moment this adventure
would have made sense for me.
Probably because I was
far too cowardly to face him.
None of that matters, Frieren.
Don't dwell on the past
when you have the present.
Find someone else.
You don't have any idea how I feel.
Please.
Your reaction tells me.
And frankly, I couldn't like you less, Sein.
Great.
Well, in that case...
So I've decided you're going
to join us no matter what.
Huh?
But why?
That makes so little sense, it's scary.
You saved me.
So toasty.
I'm truly sorry for all the
trouble that we caused you.
Please excuse us.
How much did it cost
to get everything back?
He said we should take our time
and enjoy the Harvest Festival.
Then he gave it all back to me for free.
A nice man.
It's your lucky day.
He said he didn't know
what to do with the axe.
That's kinda sad.
Here, Mr. Stark.
Put these on.
How rude!
You have to hold them like they're
too gross for your precious hands!
I believe these are yours, Mr. Sein.
Well, hell, someone's grumpy.
What'd I do to set her off?
For starters, you robbed poor
Stark of all his possessions.
I told you that wasn't me.
It was the Chief.
People who gamble
are the lowest of the low.
I get it.
I'm sorry.
And to think, that man's
supposed to be a priest.
Any priest who drinks is wrong in my book.
But Mistress Frieren, a priest once told
me that alcohol is the very best medicine.
How dare Heiter poison your young mind?
Regardless of whether he
decides to come with us or
not, I do feel that Sein
should become an adventurer.
That idea has really grown
on you since this all began.
I realized that it might be
nice to give someone the
push they need, just like
Himmel the Hero gave to me.
For whatever reason, the
adventurers decided to hang around.
Their presence has taken
up more than a bit of space.
They've been trying to recruit
me every day since their arrival.
I've tried my best to make them stop.
But my efforts have been in vain.
They invite me on adventures with cheer in
their voices and eyes full of hopes and dreams.
Like he did back then.
The plan is to travel around
the Northern Lands for a bit.
I'll be back around the
harvest three years from now.
If you aren't ready to hit the
road yet, you can join me then.
Let's go on our next adventure together.
Every time they try to recruit
me, I wonder, why now?
They radiate hope, too
bright for my tired eyes.
You want to know what Sein likes?
For what?
We can't seem to win him
over, so we're looking for ideas.
What does my brother like?
Alcohol, tobacco, and gambling
always seem to attract him.
We've gathered that much.
We're sure this guy's a priest?
Master Heiter was in good company.
All serious priests like to drink.
I'm not sure that I've
met a serious priest.
Let me see... What he adores
more than anything is older women.
How fitting of our depraved priest.
Older ladies, huh?
Thank you.
But I'm not entirely sure what
to do with that information.
Hm?
Hello?
Ah, that's right.
You're kidding me.
This sickle is too small
to use, don't you think?
It can hardly cut grass.
Oh, it's you three again.
Do you have a minute, Sein?
You're still here.
Come on.
I'm getting sick of repeating myself, kid.
Find someone else.
Say, Sein, wouldn't you like to
travel with an older lady on your arm?
Look at who you're talking to.
The thought of that very scenario was why I
wanted to be an adventurer in the first place.
What a motive.
I'm on the edge of my seat.
Where is this vixen of which you speak?
You've been looking right at her, Sein.
Did you realize I'm an elf?
As far as older women go,
I'm as old as you can get.
I knew you were an elf.
I think my brother mentioned that.
Ugh.
You're too cruel.
She hardly looks like a
woman, let alone older.
He seems so distressed.
I apologize.
I had no desire to take it to this
level, but you leave me no choice.
The time has come to use the ancient
seduction technique taught to me by my master.
What was that?
I blew you a kiss, of course.
Maybe you're too young
to appreciate it, Sonny.
Somebody take this twisted child home.
That was way too steamy for me.
What's the deal with you two?
That's odd.
When I tried the very same maneuver
on Himmel, it knocked him out cold.
Himmel!
You are a wicked woman.
How bizarre.
I'm with you.
If I had been the target of your attack,
I would have been in grave danger.
As depraved as he is, he's still
a holy man and a formidable foe.
That's enough already!
I'm not becoming an adventurer, so quit.
But I thought that you
wanted to go after your friend.
You understand my reason, brother.
Do I, Sein?
He promised me that he would
be back here in three years.
He hasn't been back for ten.
The obvious explanation is that he's dead.
So you're going to give up
without ever going to look for him?
Ten years isn't as long as you think.
The more time that you wait, the
greater and greater that number will grow.
You'll wonder if you could have
made it if you'd left town with us.
It's too... Too late, you suppose, correct?
Don't dwell in the past
when you have the present.
Sein.
I can't go.
Couldn't then, can't now.
It's been ten years and I
still have the same reason.
It's not so much that I
would miss this village.
I can't leave my brother behind.
You're scared of leaving me?
Why is that?
When Mr. Heiter came to observe
us years ago, I heard you both talking.
Your talent could take you far, my lad.
There's no doubt you could
serve as a priest in the Holy Capital.
Me?
In the Holy Capital?
Yes, without question.
That sounds great, but what would happen
to my little brother if I chose to go?
He'd come with you, of course.
Understood.
Mr. Heiter, I deeply appreciate the offer.
But my life here is just fine.
More than that, it's what my brother knows.
We tragically lost our parents
when he was young, you see.
This village is his home.
I do thank you, but I can't take
away the one comfort he has left.
Very well.
You're in a tricky situation.
I suppose I wasted my time by coming here.
But if I'm already wasting time,
perhaps I'll talk with your brother.
The little ones always get a kick
hearing the tales of my adventures.
My brother had a chance to leave
this village, but he stayed for me.
Sein, is that the reason
you've made yourself miserable?
You must see that you
and I are not the same.
The decision to stay was mine to make
and I have never in my life regretted it.
Don't pretend that you can say as much.
How long do you intend
to regret your choice?
For shame.
I apologize to my brother.
Good.
Please don't get the
wrong idea about the man.
He's kind as can be.
He's never once laid a hand on me before.
It just shows how
strongly he feels about this.
I mean, I'd never seen
that expression on his face.
Well, Frieren, you won.
I'm going to become an adventurer.
My friend might need me.
Ten years isn't as long as you think.
Well, but...
Looking for him is my main goal.
He's the reason I'm doing this.
I'll find that ape and make our
ridiculous childhood dreams come true.
I'll travel with you for now,
but hopefully I'll find him soon.
Take that, fish!
I'm impressed.
Maybe I should have asked this
before, but where are you headed?
Heaven, of course.
Is that someplace you
need to work to get to?
Well, I'll end up there when we die.
Even you'll end up there, Mr. Sein?
My, what a start.
She doesn't beat around the bush, does she?
Hey, at least you're in it with me, buddy.
Good luck to us both.