This town seems to
have a lot of nice stalls.
Agreed.
Might be worth doing some looking around.
Mere paces in and this
place is clearly full of life.
You can tell by the number of bars.
You've worked so hard.
May I take you shopping to say thanks?
This town seems to
have a lot of nice stalls.
If you want to, I suppose.
What are you doing, Frieren?
Let's get a move on!
What do you gain by being so rude?
You berate me every single chance you get!
If you hate me, just come
out and say it already!
I'm going back to my master!
Would it kill her to listen to what I have to say
once in a while before she—????!
What's all the noise about?
Lovebirds fighting?
If you weren't aware,
today is Fern's birthday.
And unfortunately, Stark
forgot to get her a gift.
She's not taking it well.
If you ask me, you were
a bit too harsh this time.
You never listen to a single
thing that poor lad has to say.
To be honest, I didn't
get you anything either.
When it comes to us men, we couldn't
care less about trivial dates, you know.
Anniversaries, birthdays... That hurt!
I get it!
Okay, I'll go pick up a trinket
for your birthday if you'll stop!
At least spare my knees!
After that beating, I feel
even more sorry for him.
I'm old enough now not to make a
big stink if somebody hurts my feelings.
But a girl like you has the power to stir up
the emotions of a boy like him into a whirlwind.
My advice is to go after the kid.
That might be my advice too.
I think her hair ornament
has a butterfly on it, too.
A cute pouch you've got there.
You don't like it?
I don't like how used to keeping
the company of women you seem.
Of course.
So, did you ever find Stark?
I spotted him in the plaza.
Couldn't bring yourself
to talk to him, could you?
I understand.
It's not that you don't like the guy.
You just aren't used to keeping
the company of men your own age.
Oh, to be young.
No matter.
Choose whatever you want.
We can take a look at
some other shops, too.
Thanks, but that's quite alright.
Fine, guess I'll choose on my own.
Anyway, if he did forget to get you
something, don't take it personally.
He doesn't strike me as
the conscientious type.
I doubt there are many years he
even remembers his own birthday.
Don't blame the fool.
He didn't have to remember
because I gave him a present on it.
Right.
You picked out one together, didn't you?
How did you know that?
Most people wouldn't decline when someone
offers to buy them whatever they want.
You must already have some birthday
shopping memory you consider sacred.
That's why you told me no.
I guess that could be.
I don't know about Sacred,
but it did feel like the right choice.
I believe it.
Now, apologize to Stark, then you two
can pick out the best president in town.
Sure, he's slow on the
uptake, but he's just a kid.
You want to make up with him, yes?
Remember that people can't
know how you feel until you tell them.
Guess you're right.
I'm gonna head back to the inn now.
One thing.
I'm sorry about all the kicking.
Mr. Stark.
Fern...
I...
Sorry!
I wanted to choose a gift with
you to make sure you'd love it.
But after you got upset, I didn't want it to look
like I was trying to dig myself out of a hole.
So I didn't say anything.
Because I got nervous and I was worried
you might become even more mad at me.
That wouldn't have made
me mad in the slightest.
Mr. Stark, would you forgive me?
I was too harsh with you.
Please.
I've grown used to it.
I really am sorry, though.
You ready to shop?
Yeah.
Spying on the sweethearts?
That's in poor taste, Frieren.
You're doing the same.
I'm just glad that they made up.
The older you get, the better you start understanding relationships,
and the better you can do that, the fewer conflicts arise.
Arguments like that are
a privilege of the young.
This can't have been easy for you, Frieren.
Looking after two kids all alone.
You understand relationships?
Make that three kids.
It struck me as odd Fern turned
to me for advice instead of you.
A girl wouldn't do that unless she has
someone in her past she's comparing me to.
You do know Fern was
raised by Heiter, don't you?
That's the last person I
should be compared to.
He was a great priest.
Great isn't the word I would use.
When he wasn't drunk,
he was deathly hungover.
He's gone undead on us.
He was terribly picky with his food.
Quit it, Heiter.
And he lied more often than not.
I haven't had a drop all day.
He was a corrupt priest, plain and simple.
Though I admit, your
depravity far exceeds his.
Yeah, sorry about that.
All that stuff is hard to believe.
Sounds nothing like the Heiter I remember.
He was a kind, dependable,
and upright old man.
A proper grown-up.
The very opposite of what I've become.
The years have changed you, Heiter.
You've grown dignified.
To me, that sounds like
a nice way of saying old.
A certain level of maturity
comes naturally as we age.
Or rather, that's what I wish I could say.
Truth is, though my body has grown and shrunk,
my mind has hardly changed since I was a child.
I've pretended to be an adult all my life.
Though I might look the part now, not
a bit of adulthood has stirred within me.
I'd like to be a proper grown-up,
but I fear I'll pretend until I die.
It's important that children have adults.
Little ones can't thrive
without emotional support.
Fern is the hard-working sort.
She needs a lot of
guidance and a lot of praise.
If you're still a child, then shouldn't
you be praised for maintaining this ruse?
Where's the grown-up to praise you?
She's up above somewhere
waiting for me to join her.
I'll have to venture into heaven
before I receive my reward.
Well, while you're still here,
I could always praise you.
You'd do that for me?
How kind.
But I doubt you understand just how
a withering human like me might feel.
So how do you intend to praise me?
I must admit that was
much nicer than I expected.
Frieren, once I get to Heaven, I'll
have a word with the Goddess for you.
When you join me, you should
be praised by her too, my friend.
Oh?
Then I'll look forward to it.
What do you think you're doing, Frieren?
In my opinion, you're as
proper as grown-ups come, Sein.
If only you were an older lady.
This moment would be perfect.
You should be glad then.
Precious few women are older than me.
Thank you, sir.
This area has an extreme
deficit of passenger carriages.
We must all help our
fellow men in times of need.
I work as a merchant, selling
my wares in the town up ahead.
I supply the people there
with fine accessories.
Look at my stock, if you'd like.
You're quite the salesman, aren't you?
Alas, finer things are lost on me.
My apprentice Fern may
be interested, though.
Huh?
Did you buy a new bracelet?
Well, uh, kind of.
That's a pretty design.
I have a ring with the
very same pattern on it.
It was a gift from Himmel
for a job well done.
I think it would match perfectly.
I've never seen it.
Let me think.
Where did I put that thing?
Under here?
Goodness, you're so disorganized.
Finally.
Sorry, I let my guard down.
Avian monsters are cunning beasts
and very skilled at concealing their mana.
What to do?
Let's defeat the monster
and then figure something out.
You mages use magic
to fly around all the time.
You can make a carriage
float for a bit, can't you?
Think, Stark.
Have you ever seen a
flying carriage before?
Yeah, we're in one right now.
This may come as a surprise, but it has only been 40
short years since humankind first learned how to fly.
Until then, the skies were the exclusive
domain of demons and monsters.
The flying magic you see us use today is actually
a demon spell mankind was able to repurpose.
Nobody's looking for a lecture, okay?
So can you make the
carriage levitate or not?
We can't adapt their spell because we've merely
copied the how without understanding the why.
Things larger than humans can
only be made to fly in short spurts.
You should've led with that.
We'll have to abandon ship.
I'll fly out with our new merchant
ally, and Fern, you leave with Sein.
Understood, ma'am.
I'll get my cargo together.
Uh, hey, uh, and me?
I figured that you could jump down.
What are you talking about?
Pretty sure a fall like that would kill me.
Surely a warrior can
handle a fall from this height.
Don't look at me like I'm crazy!
You know good and well that
would snap every bone in my body!
You really think it would?
Eisen could free fall from any height
without getting so much as a scratch.
What is wrong with this man?
Heiter was appalled.
Yet another story that goes to show
how far from normal Mr. Eisen is.
Perhaps we can levitate the carriage for a
moment, just before it crashes into the forest.
I'd need to calculate if I have
the power to stop a free fall.
If I can't sufficiently reduce the force of
our plummet, we'd be ground into minced meat.
Why'd you have to say it all scary-like?
Whatever it is that we do,
we should probably do it quick.
This type of monster kills its
prey by slamming it into the ground.
Well, I suppose her idea is worth a shot.
You better not drop us!
We're alive!
Indeed.
Indicating our plan was a success.
You call that a success?
What's worse is she called it a plan.
Your horse was only slightly
injured, but I fixed it up for you.
The greater concern is your carriage.
It needs major repairs.
Sorry.
Please, don't apologize.
I'm thankful.
If it had just been me,
I would surely be dead.
It's gonna take some
time to fix the carriage.
Huh?
It should be right here.
I wonder where it went.
It's gotten a lot warmer lately.
Might be time to start dressing lighter.
Oh, by the way, Fern, about
that bracelet... Oh, right.
This is what Mr. Stark
got me for my birthday.
I spent three whole
hours picking out that thing.
So you ended up being the one to choose?
I wanted him to pick whatever
he thought would be best.
Yeah, should've seen that coming.
She put you through the ringer, huh?
Her type is the hardest to deal with.
Truth.
What about this one?
Three hours of trying
to gauge her reactions.
I felt like I was dying inside.
You poor soul.
I can hear everything they're saying.
Oh, well.
It was all worth it since
she likes it so much.
Attaboy.
To tell you the truth, I didn't think you had
it in you to make such a romantic statement.
That design is of a mirrored lotus.
In the language of flowers,
it means eternal love.
Around these parts, it's a
common symbol to give to a lover.
Mr. Stark?
I had no idea, okay?
It's all a misunderstanding.
You think I've got the first clue
about the language of flowers?
No, of course not.
You're an idiot.
You're being even meaner than usual.
Not like you're some flower genius either.
What did you just say to me?
Nothing, ma'am.
So, uh, should I find
something to replace it?
You put an incredible amount of effort
into picking out the perfect gift for me.
Don't suggest such a thing again.
I wouldn't dream of it.
Something funny?
No, not at all.
Mistress Frieren.
We finished repairing the carriage.
We'll depart early tomorrow morning.
Understood.
You've been sneaking away from us at night.
What is it that you're looking for?
The ring Himmel gave me.
Let me help.
We'll wait to leave for
town until we've found it.
That's all right.
If we don't have any luck
tonight, then I'll give up.
I've grown used to losing things.
Besides, that ring isn't all that
Himmel gave me over the years.
The design.
It has a mirrored lotus
like my bracelet does.
In flower language,
that means eternal love.
I didn't realize that.
It doesn't matter.
I seriously doubt Himmel
knew what it meant either.
Regardless, I'm certain it's important.
Let's look for it together.
I wish you would have told me sooner.
Given my line of work, I'm typically the first stop
when folks in my village lose valuable jewelry.
This is a spell for
finding lost accessories.
I was intending to give it to you as a reward for
all your assistance with my carriage and horse.
Frieren.
To say a special thanks for all your hard work on
that side quest, please choose whatever you'd like.
Jewelry, huh?
I would have preferred something
from a magic shop, but this one will do.
That was too easy.
You should put some more thought into it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Frieren.
Ah, yes.
You were close to giving up your search.
Glad you didn't?
Maybe I am.
I meant to ask, why exactly are
you wearing a mirrored lotus bracelet?
Because Mr. Stark is an idiot.
No respect.