Long-range magic is a fickle
thing and rather difficult to master.
Success requires a combination of three key
factors that are essential to all mages.
There's the amount of mana utilized, the strength at which
it's fired, and the level of control you have over it.
But you know that much, correct?
Yes.
Earlier, your magic dissipated
before it reached its target.
That tells me your levels of mana
and your firing strength are both lacking.
These are not issues
that one can fix overnight.
Regardless of your talent, such
skills will take years to master.
That said, the level of control you
have over your magic is very high.
That's the area where most people tend to struggle,
but you're already exhibiting great strength there.
My advice is to be patient with yourself.
All right.
Frieren, Himmel, Heiter, Eisen, Flamme, Serie, Denken,
Übel, Land, Wirbel, Richter, Kanne, Lawine, Draht, Solitär.
Is Fern's training coming along smoothly?
In a short four years, she's
learned more than most do in ten.
I don't feel this is a good thing.
She is studying too hard.
Perhaps.
Nothing seems to pull her out of the woods.
Even so, I'm glad she's
found something she loves.
Regardless, she's still a long
way from becoming a proper mage.
I'll have deciphered the grimoire
before she reaches that status.
Is that so?
You know, Heiter, the odds this text
contains anything pertaining to... Heiter?
You can wipe that
look of pity off your face.
I consider the fact I stayed on
my feet for so long a minor miracle.
I will try to be quick with my work.
Thank you, my friend.
Fern, I need you with Heiter.
He collapsed.
Put your training on hold.
But I still haven't shot
through the boulder.
I have no doubt you'll
achieve it eventually.
Right now, we— It cannot be eventually!
When eventually comes, Master
Heiter will have passed away.
Man saved my life, you know.
Throwing away your life
now would be an utter waste.
A waste, mister?
A long time ago, I lost someone too.
He was a dear companion
whom I cherished very much.
His heart was made of gold
and his nerves made of steel.
He would sooner sacrifice his
life than abandon someone in need.
If he was still here, and I was the one six feet
below, more innocent lives could have been saved.
Since I'm not the type for such selflessness, I
planned to live out the rest of my days quietly.
But before I could hole up
for good, I realized something.
If I sat and died in silence, all I learned about friendship, strength of will, and
courage, all the precious memories we had made, they would vanish like they had never been.
If there is even one precious memory tucked within the walls
of your mind, then I think it would be a waste for you to die.
Master Heiter fears dying now more
than ever, because it means I'll be alone.
I have to show him he did
the right thing back then.
Saving my life can't be his final regret.
I don't care if it's as a
mage or whatever else.
Learning some kind of skill to support
myself is my way of repaying him.
He's the reason I'm here, and I need
him to know I'll be alright when he's gone.
Do you remember everything
that I've taught you so far?
Yes.
Good.
Then do as you like.
Scherzo.
There weren't any spells for bringing
back the dead or granting immortality.
Worth a try.
Did you know that?
An immeasurable fear
of death lives within us all.
If such spells did exist, Eivig most
surely would have cast them on himself.
Then why bother?
How's Frieren?
Is she growing strong?
She has room to improve in some areas, but it
wouldn't be incorrect to call her a proper mage.
Excellent.
So she made it in time.
It'll be hard for you to say she'll
get in your way, now, won't it?
Will you bring her with you
and strengthen her skills?
Forgive me, Heiter, but I must draw a line.
She would only get in my way.
You deceived me, didn't you?
Your payment for decrypting
the grimoire is in the desk.
I must ask you to leave this place tonight.
For what reason?
I'm sure you can see that I'm
not much longer for this world.
At such a young age, that child has already experienced
more than enough loss to last the rest of her lifetime.
Frieren, please take care of Fern for me.
No point in feigning courage again.
Not now.
She has been ready to say
goodbye to you for a long while.
Your only focus before you die should be giving her a
proper farewell and making as many memories as you can.
Oh, Frieren, you really are a kind girl.
So, why did you save Fern?
Because that is what Himmel,
the hero, would have done.
You're right.
A good guiding voice.
Perhaps I'll listen as well.
I really can't thank you enough.
Without your help and guidance, I
couldn't have repaid Master Heiter.
Then you should be
thanking him for deceiving me.
So long, corrupt priest.
Well, shall we be off?
Stop there, Fern.
That's plenty.
Thank you kindly for your help.
As for your payment, take this.
We've been doing such simple work lately.
Thus is the nature of adventuring.
What did we get paid in this time?
More folk magic.
It's a spell that produces warm tea.
We'll have to try this out later.
The other day we learned a spell
that cleans rust from bronze statues.
And before that, there was the
one for turning sweet grapes sour.
You keep collecting the strangest spells.
That is my hobby.
It sounds to me like you really
do love magic, Mistress Frieren.
Only somewhat.
The same as you.
I, uh, feel we're a bit different.
We're the same.
You're absolutely sure you
wouldn't mind doing me a favor?
As an herbalist, I can't say I have
any spells to teach you in return.
That's alright.
Any information we can learn
on local flora is helpful enough.
There he is.
A statue of Himmel the Hero.
The poor boy is in terrible shape.
I would clean him myself, but
it's too much for one old lady.
And I can't convince
the other villagers to care.
When the village was attacked by a vicious monster, the
brave Mr. Himmel fought with all his might to defend us.
Such a hero should be
revered, not left to crumble.
Perhaps.
But not in Himmel's case.
It's only fair that he pays for his pride.
When the villagers offered to make a statue
of him, he should have humbly declined.
How is this?
You don't think it's too handsome, right?
He spent 18 hours choosing a
pose, driving the poor sculptor mad.
All of that debate, and they settled
on something ridiculously ordinary.
I've never heard that before.
Come to think of it, there was an elven
mage in the hero's party, wasn't there?
So, shall we clean him up?
Thank you so much.
Magic is an incredible thing.
There isn't a speck of
rust anywhere in sight.
I do wish there was a bit
more color around here, though.
I'll have to plant some flowers soon.
We could do that.
You have a spell that
produces flowers, don't you?
Yes, indeed.
I suppose I could conjure something.
No, blue moon weed flowers would be best.
I can't recall that one.
What do they look like?
I don't know.
I've never seen them.
Then why those?
Because they grow in Himmel's hometown.
You can't conjure flowers
you haven't seen before.
Blue Moonweed.
Haven't heard that name in years.
Long ago, a beautiful lush field of them
used to bloom right outside my house.
So they don't grow here anymore?
Seems they died off on us.
It's been several decades now since
they were last spotted in these lands.
Fern, let's go.
Coming.
You're hiding something.
Whatever it is, I won't be upset.
Found friends, did you?
I believe they're seed rats.
I'll take them outside.
Well, Fern, shall our moon
weed quest commence?
Are you joking, Mistress?
Why would I be?
She said there was a
field of them right here.
Decades ago.
But they're well worth looking for.
If we're able to find and analyze them, we
can conjure Blue Moon Weed wherever we like.
You're doing this for Himmel's sake?
Oh no.
I believe I'm doing it for my own.
Mistress Frieren, we've scoured
these woods for six months.
I don't think we're going to find it.
You're right.
Perhaps it's time we broaden
the radius of our quest.
Oh, I don't often see you on your own.
It's been quite a while since
you two first arrived in this village.
So, have you found any Blue Moon Weed?
Is our search a lost cause?
She's so quick to fixate on
anything relating to magic.
By the looks of it, she's going to continue
this hunt for years, if not decades.
Given her strength as a mage, she has
the power to save whole cities of people.
She shouldn't spend her time
looking for something so tiny.
Something that may not exist.
You're so young, child.
Is that simply a polite way
of saying you think I'm wrong?
No, and I don't disagree with you.
But you see, Miss Frieren likely
views things differently than you and me.
And because she's so much more mature than
us, I'm sure she'd understand your feelings.
If you say how you feel with an open
heart, I've no doubt she'll take it well.
They're the seeds of a related species
she kept for their medicinal properties.
Would it be alright if we planted
these around Himmel's statue instead?
I hear you, Fern.
And I see I've made you worry.
The time I spend isn't
solely my own anymore.
We should go.
I promise that I'll end my search soon.
Mistress, how many years is soon?
Ah, soon enough.
Please, no.
That's not comforting, coming-Shhh.
Shall we see where it's heading?
I've been wanting to ask, why do
you collect spells in the first place?
It's just a hobby of mine.
That's quite hard to believe.
It's a hobby, and a good one.
I used to go through my life much
more apathetically before finding it.
Gross.
But then came a fool who
praised me for the magic I acquired.
The rest is history.
That's a pretty silly reason.
I agree.
Is that... A flower petal.
They say seed rats store their food by burying
it in safe places away from their enemies.
They're clever little critters, aren't they?
I wouldn't say that.
They bury their food all over, so they
often forget where they hide their reserves.
Blue Moonweed?
A flower grown in my homeland.
They're truly beautiful.
To be fair, they grow pretty heroes too.
Shall we get going then?
Frieren, I'd like to show you them someday.
Sure, if the chance arises.
I had a feeling we'd find them
here, but I wasn't expecting this.
Seems the chance arose.
At last.
I can't believe that
we actually found them.
Now we can create a spell
to conjure Blue Moon Weed.
It's evident how important magic is to you.
I don't understand why.
Yes, you do.
Becoming a mage was a challenge,
but you never once wanted to give up.
That's very different.
I could have learned any other skill that allowed
me to support myself and been just as content.
It didn't have to be magic.
No.
But it's what you chose.
I guess you're right.
Blue Mood Weed.
I thought I would never see it again.
It looks beautiful.
Thank you for your diligence, Miss Frieren.
You've ensured that time will never
get the better of the statue again.
Oh, I nearly forgot.
There.
Look at that!
An adorable touch.
Well, shall we be off?