Flamme?
You mean Master.
What is it?
Do you really think the way
you dealt with them was unfair?
Frieren, do you remember Basalt's
final words before he perished?
Why would I bother?
Their kind only uses
words to deceive.
Smart girl.
They are nothing more than monsters
that can imitate the human tongue.
I call them demons, and take it
from an expert, they are all the same.
They don't play fair, so we have no choice
but to take their lead and deceive doubly so.
If this could be the secret to exterminating their species,
then I will gladly embrace the dishonor it entails.
The bleeding won't stop.
This is the end.
It would seem your plan
has failed rather badly.
Yes, perhaps.
But Frieren won't
make it out unscathed.
By this hour, I'm sure she and
Lady Aura have begun to clash.
Decades ago, we were forced
to retreat by the Party of Heroes.
But this time, she has
no heroes to hide behind.
I do admit your ally poses a threat to
us, but her mana is no match for my lady's.
If Frieren attacks her head on,
she'll most certainly lose the fight.
In that case, I have no
doubt my mistress will win.
She would never directly engage a demon,
especially not one that's so powerful.
She'll kill Aura
by tricking her.
Nonsense.
I know this mage.
Frieren the Slayer has never
once fought us from the shadows.
Why then do I feel
something is wrong?
This girl's mana is weak.
Yet I was overwhelmed by the
sheer number of her rapid attacks.
How was she able to execute such
powerful magic without exhausting her mana?
I see.
Is such a thing even possible?
So Frieren does the same?
Too afraid to fight fair?
Both you and your teacher are
a disgrace to the title of mage.
I assure you Mistress Frieren
knows that better than anyone else.
What horrors await today?
This is an Elven village.
Basalt the Throne.
A general of the
Demon King's army.
He must have led his forces
here to destroy this town.
Speak up, girl.
Was it you who killed him?
You look near dead yourself.
Good bit of mana you have there.
You must be powerful.
You took them
head on, didn't you?
A brute in disguise.
That was a foolish mistake.
I don't know why people
prefer an honest playing field.
Run or hide, or take
them by surprise.
You're working both
safer and smarter if you do.
I can't understand the
way strong mages think.
Well, you should.
Huh?
You should understand
exactly how I think.
I'm certain you are far
more powerful a mage than I.
And what makes you say that?
Call it a hunch.
Interesting.
Have a name?
What happened to the village?
Its people are dead.
Not even the women
and children were spared.
I couldn't save them.
Being their strongest
didn't do me any good.
Trying to save
them at all was silly.
If it were me, one side of those
monsters would have sent me for the hills.
Put me down.
No.
You have potential.
You're going to
be my apprentice.
Don't forget I saved your life.
If I hadn't shown up, you would
be sharing a grave with that demon.
You failed to protect your
village and nearly yourself.
You would have died in vain.
But luckily, I was
there to assist.
Behind us.
These are stronger than
the general you killed.
Fascinating
creatures, aren't they?
They fully intended to catch us off guard by
concealing their mana until just before they struck.
But the moment they realized we were mages,
they waltzed out into the open with grandeur.
They are cunning and
they never play fair.
But every last one of them has a ridiculous
sense of pride when it comes to magic.
You may leave, human mage.
Once you put down
the elf girl, that is.
And you'll let me go
free if I do as you say.
Massacre the elves.
Now.
Those were the
Demon King's orders.
Your existence
matters not to me.
How thoughtful.
Frieren, you were right before.
I'm painfully aware of how
a powerful mage thinks.
Much like I'm aware of
how these creatures think.
I know the absolute faith they have in these
magics they've poured their lives into studying.
In other words, I know they're an
arrogant and overconfident breed.
Frieren, they lacked your perception
and quickly judged me a weakling.
Though I admit they were exceptional mages,
their overconfidence cost them their lives.
By controlling the release of your mana, you hid
your strength so they didn't see you as a threat.
That's right.
I deceive and kill my enemies by
allowing them to miscalculate my power.
It is a cowardly and unfair way to fight that
makes a mockery of the art of magic itself.
Your injuries are
looking much better.
I'd say it's time we
begin your training.
Flamme?
You mean Master.
The demons took all that
I've ever known from me.
Me too.
I wish to eradicate
every last one.
Me too.
But I love magic and
hold great respect for it.
You and I are the same.
That's why we should be the only
ones who can make a mockery of it.
Protect it through cowardice.
What do you suppose
I should do to train?
Try limiting the mana you release
to one-tenth of its typical volume.
Impressive.
You're controlling it well.
I imagine any elf could
do something so simple.
While you do that, we'll
spend time on fundamentals.
Work to raise the
base of your mana.
Is that really all?
Easy enough.
Do I stop suppressing my mana whenever
I feel like it, or whenever you tell me to?
It'll get tiring if I
do it for too long.
You'll do it for
as long as I have.
For life.
If you can, you'll fool Daemonkind
for the rest of your days.
I sense Lord Lügner is dead.
Slaughtered like the
rest of your executioners.
Do you see your failure, Aura?
That I do.
'Tis a shame indeed.
However, if I defeat you here and now,
their sacrifice won't have been for naught.
At the beginning of our skirmish, you made it your priority to
release as many immortal soldiers from my control as you could.
All that work cost you.
Was it wise to expend so much
of your mana right in front of me?
The scales of obedience.
When two souls are placed opposite each other,
whichever has more mana forces the other to submit.
Only someone with as much mana as Aura could
handle this sort of risky magic so casually.
Generally speaking, a person's mana increases
in proportion to time spent training.
I can feel it in the
power pouring off her.
She's a great demon who has lived for over 500 years
and has spent the majority of that time training.
500 years.
That's fairly
long-lived for her kind.
I doubt she's been
challenged before.
I can tell that much from the
mana overflowing from her body.
She has no tricks up her sleeve,
as demons don't conceal their mana.
They can't afford to.
I pity you.
Aselyse.
Master?
Demons are quite cunning
creatures, are they not?
So why haven't they thought to
constantly suppress their mana like you do?
I'm sure they
would if they could.
Demons are individualists by nature, but form the frailest
connections needed to stand a chance against humankind.
The barest society
needs what to function?
Order, I suppose.
That's right.
Even an organization of monsters
needs someone of importance to lead it.
Humans need the same.
Importance is determined
by status and wealth.
In our world, those who
have both get to rule.
Look at that well-dressed
fellow leaving the palace.
He's clearly important.
But humans have no
innate way of showing that.
So, for others to know he's someone of note,
he has to put on the trappings of rank.
So demons are different, then.
Despite their performance of civilization,
demons haven't changed a bit since beasthood.
Might makes right.
Far more straightforward
than us humans.
You can tell who's
strong by looking at them.
Through their mana?
Mana is everything
to their kind.
Much like status and
wealth are to ours.
It's dignity itself.
Now, there is a chance they may temporarily
suppress their mana for the sake of stealth,
but none are foolish enough to forfeit their
standing to constantly suppress their power.
It's the difference between a noble
sneaking out into town in disguise and
that same noble debasing themselves
by abandoning their station entirely.
Demons know nothing of charity and would
never grant dignity to those with little mana.
Their world is a
cold and cruel one.
So, the stronger an individual is, the
more desperate they are to show it off.
Unlike us, for them there's no benefit
in constantly suppressing their mana.
The thought doesn't so
much as cross their minds.
In a way, I pity them.
Just as we are bound by the places we live and the
clothing we can afford, demons are bound by mana.
Magic is the very lifeblood of their species, but for all their
unrivaled love for it, the poor fools can't even control their mana.
Frieren, you're very
lucky you aren't a demon.
I know I am.
I couldn't deceive
them if I were.
It's been three years since you
began suppressing your mana.
I suppose I was right
about you after all.
You've grown
much better at that.
Now tell me, you still
love magic, don't you?
That was rather out
of the blue, Master.
But yes, somewhat.
Your confidence
has waned over time.
Long ago, you told me you
loved the craft with fervor.
It's only been fifty
years since then.
A smart girl.
All this time, and the only thing I've
taught my apprentice to do is fight.
Magic fit for revenge.
Is that something you regret?
Not a bit.
No one's better suited to hold on
to the secrets of my magic than you.
You're going to
live a long life.
Perhaps someday you'll become
strong enough to defeat the Demon King.
Frieren, I do have one request.
What is it?
All I ask is that you plant
flowers around my grave.
That doesn't seem like you.
I know.
Frieren, I have a spell that
creates a field of flowers.
To tell you the truth, it's
actually my favorite one.
My parents taught it
to me when I was a girl.
It's what made me
fall in love with magic.
Then I'd like you
to teach it to me.
Listen to me, Frieren.
You must never seek to
leave your mark on history.
There's safety in obscurity.
And once you've finally defeated the Demon King,
rest assured the whole world shall know your name.
I've heard a seasoned mage
lives somewhere in these woods.
Is that mage you?
Seasoned in the sense
I've been around, perhaps.
But I've done precious
little with my years.
I'm in no way exceptional.
What do you think, Heiter?
I would say she has approximately
one-fifth of the mana I do.
Fairly middle of the road.
Way to make a first impression.
Now move along.
You don't have business
with a mediocre mage, do you?
No, but you're easily the strongest
mage I've ever laid eyes on.
And what would
make you say that?
Call it a hunch.
Aselyse.
You seem awfully
happy with yourself.
Are you so certain
you'll win, Aura?
We'll find out soon enough.
Frieren the Slayer.
It's been 80 years since you made your
first meaningful appearance in this world.
With a party of heroes, you
defeated the Demon King.
It makes one wonder just how
long you've had to study your magic.
Unfortunately for you, it matters not how
many years you've managed to survive.
Your mana tells me
everything I need to know.
I can see it clearly.
There is no question you are an exceptional
mage, but your mana itself is unimpressive.
I would wager you've had no
more than a hundred years training.
Not only that, it's been eighty
years and you haven't grown a bit.
Were you honing other skills
instead of increasing your mana?
Or were you piddling
your life away?
Just as expected.
You are absolutely
no match for me.
As you can see, I win.
I shall consider it an honor to
sever the head of the Slayer myself.
I'm shocked that it wasn't even
necessary to exhaust her mana.
I needn't have been so cautious.
Though she did defeat a
decent amount of my troops.
I'll have to
replenish them later.
What's this?
The scales are starting
to tip in her direction.
You're the one who opted
to gamble with my soul, Aura.
To tell you the truth, I would have been in real
trouble if you had tried to overwhelm me with numbers.
I'm grateful for your overconfidence
when it comes to your mana.
Now I can finally defeat you.
Oh, can you now?
You really should
have figured it out.
I've been suppressing my mana.
A grave miscalculation
on your part, Aura.
Valiant last-ditch effort, but there's no
chance that could have escaped my notice.
There wasn't a hint of the instability or variation
in your mana output that comes with suppression.
I'm surprised.
Demons are capable of
observing mana with such accuracy.
Seems my master was
right in her methods after all.
I've spent the better part of my life
in a constant state of suppression.
It has become natural for me.
You're dimmer than I thought.
Why would you ever
do something so foolish?
Foolish, yes.
But powerful.
It lets me defeat your kind.
This is absurd!
I'm a great demon who
has lived for over 500 years!
Aura, the one standing before you, is a
great mage who's lived for over a thousand.
Frieren, just as demons deceive mankind with
their words, you must deceive them with your mana.
Aura, kill yourself.
This can't be... No...
How could I ever...