Hope you're ready for me, 'cause I'm comin' through!
It's all so infuriating!
Teruko!
Hold on to the furniture!
That demon has special powers!
You shouldn't be attacking so recklessly!
How maddening,
all these cursed insects running amok in my house.
I can't believe the room spun around!
Now, this is what I call a fun time!
Get your dirty feet off of her!
Who the hell are you, kid?
Stepping on a little kid like that!
What are you thinking?!
You got spunk. I like that.
Having a human send me flying, that's a first for me!
Why is he coming after me?
Isn't he a demon slayer?
These swords do a lot of damage.
They're not the kind you
delicate little flowers would use.
The way they shred through flesh
is what I pride myself on the most.
This is foolish! There's a demon right there!
You think I care?! Hah!
Measly insects.
You're irksome. Now die!
The floor just ripped apart.
It happened at the speed of the beat of the drum
and in the shape of a beast's claws!
Rotating right.
Back left.
Insects.
Miserable vermin!
I'm starting to understand.
We're in another room now?
But that demon didn't strike his drum,
so what does this mean?
I'm picking up the scent of multiple demons in this house.
Is there another demon with a drum, then?
Is that why
I can smell blood.
It's gonna be fine.
You just stay behind me.
Another human mauled and eaten.
Is something wrong?
No, we're fine. There's no demons.
Come on. Let's head out.
Keep your eyes forward, all right? Don't look behind you.
I smell something else,
a unique scent of blood that I've never smelled before.
Seems like there wasn't much bleeding.
Excuse me. Can we stop, Zenitsu?
You gotta warn me first before you speak up!
You can't go surprising me like that here!
My heart nearly jumped out of my mouth just now!
Sorry about that.
If I had a heart attack, you
would have been directly responsible!
You'd be a murderer! Do you understand?!
Well, it's just that...
You've been sweating, gasping, and shivering really badly.
What about it?!
I'm doing the best I can here, all right?!
Um, forgive me for saying so,
but you're making me really nervous, too.
Oh, no! I'm sorry!
It's just I feel if we make too much noise here,
that demon you saw,
it might find us, right?
That's why I think it would be best to
be as quiet as possible! Don't you think?!
A couple of kids.
I bet you'll taste delicious.
What did I tell you?!
It's just my luck we'd run into a demon!
Stay away! Stay away from us! I'm warning you!
W-we don't taste good!
I'm sure I taste awful! I'm serious!
This kid's all skin and bones,
so he'd be dry and taste terrible!
How will I know for sure until I have a lick?
Are you kidding me?! His tongue
is like a bolt of lighting!
This has to be a nightmare!
Zenitsu, you've gotta get up!
My knees! My fear is in my knees!
This isn't the time to complain about that stuff!
Just leave me behind, okay? Make a run for it!
I can't do something like that.
What a sweet kid.
As useless as I am, he's sticking by me.
I gotta find a solution to this.
If I don't protect him, I don't
wanna think of what'll happen.
Dying before he reaches adulthood would be tragic.
But I'm so horribly weak.
Get up!
I don't have the strength to protect him.
But, if I don't, then that would mean
I'm going to relish using my tongue to
scoop your brains out through your ears.
Zenitsu!
Are you...
He's asleep.
What's up with him?
Die!
Please wake up!
Zenitsu!
Wh-what is this sound?
This boy, he's not the same as before.
Zenitsu?
Thunder breathing...
First form.
Thunderclap and flash.
It's dead?!
When did that happen?! What the hell?! This is weird!
What is this? Yuck!
Shoichi, did... did you just...
You saved me! Thank you so much!
I'll never forget that you did this!
Why didn't you just tell me from
the start that you were so powerful?!
What are you talking about?
You say something?
Huh? No.
It's nothing.
We should go now.
Yeah.
Damn it! He sent me flying again!
These last three days, it's been the same old crap.
I don't like making my way
through a cramped building like this!
It's just not my thing.
You dodged that.
You seem quite spry, human.
Your healthy flesh will be well worth gouging out to eat!
Self-taught style, beast breathing!
It's gonna feel so good to rip
such a huge target to shreds!
You've got a lot of guts to charge me head-on like that!
Revel in your own death, and serve as my catalyst!
Fang three, devour!
Coming through! Coming through!
Marechi, I need it.
To devour even one,
I would have as many as 50... Nay, 100 bodies worth.
I must search for more humans
with Marechi and devour them.
In doing so, I will be able to
reclaim my place among the Twelve Kizuki.
Kyogai.
Why have you stopped eating?
Have you reached your limit?
No, sir. I can go on!
P-Please! Give me just a little more time.
I think not.
I am stripping you of your number,
because you have nothing more to offer me.
The more humans you devour, the stronger you become.
Once he saw my potential,
master Kibutsuji was willing to share his blood with me.
The power of that man's blood was simply astonishing.
I was sure that I'd grow
infinitely stronger than ever before
and recognized into the ranks of the Twelve Kizuki.
I would continue to gorge myself on humans
and steadily become even more powerful!
Or so I believed.
Kiyoshi, we found you!
Brother! Brother!
Teruko!
Who is he?
Tanjiro Kamado,
and I'm a demon slayer.
You two have hung in there really well.
Can you show me your wounds?
Why, Kiyoshi?
This ointment here is really amazing!
My master gave it to me for a time like this!
Wanna know something funny?
He always wears a tengu mask.
A tengu? Really?
It's the truth.
Anyway, this ointment is fantastic.
You'll feel better right away.
That'll do it!
Well? You feel better?
Yes.
Tell me exactly what happened if you can.
A monster dragged me away, and...
It nearly ate me.
Mm, but then...
Another one showed up out of nowhere.
They started fighting to the death over...
Who was gonna get to e-eat me.
Then...
The demon with the drums growing out of him...
Left one of the drums behind
after he was defeated by the others.
When I picked it up and hit it, the room changed.
That's how I held out.
A demon with drums growing from him? That guy?
He said, I think, something about "Marechi."
Yes, that's right!
I don't know what it means, but he called me that!
The term "Marechi" refers to
the owner of a rare type of blood!
What's that look?
I'll teach you respect!
Cut it out!
When you say, "rare blood," wh-what do you mean?
The blood of all living species
can be broken into types, you see?
The more scarce the blood...
Or the more uncommon it is, I should say...
The more desirable it is to demons,
for, you see, in terms of nutritional value for a demon,
a human Marechi is akin to eating
as many as a hundred normal humans.
A Marechi is like a bountiful feast
for them, a delicacy for the ages.
Marechi. Marechi.
I'm gonna head out there.
Keep calm. It's all right.
I'm going to take down that demon.
Teruko, listen to me.
Huh?
Your brother is really worn out at the
moment, so watch after him, all right?
Soon as I leave this room,
use the drum to change areas,
just like Kiyoshi's been doing.
If someone tries to open the door or you hear something,
strike that drum to remove yourself from danger.
I promise that I'll come for you.
I'll follow your scent back.
Then I'll call your names so you know it's me.
Just hold out a little longer.
Can you do it?
Great! So brave!
I'm off.
Strike it!
Damn insects. So infuriating!
The right drum flips the room right.
The left one flips it left.
Right leg, forward spin!
Left leg, backward spin!
The drum on his belly launches that claw attack!
So fast.
The speed of the rotations and attacks are brutal!
Miss Tamayo did treat my wounds,
but these injuries aren't fully healed yet.
Can I... can I beat him?
I'm in so much pain.
I don't know how much longer I can hold on!
This whole time, I've just been grinning and bearing it.
When I pulled Zenitsu off that girl he was chasing,
when I shouted at him out of anger,
I was enduring the most terrible pain.
I had to withstand it.
It was my duty as the eldest son of my family.
Whenever I tense up, my broken bones ache,
stopping me from mustering any strength.
That demon's attack is leaving
tears that look like claw marks.
I'm too scared to move in closer.
If I charge forward to get within striking distance,
I'm afraid that a flash of pain will make me falter.
If that happens
I'll be torn to shreds.
I can't help but imagine the most awful things.
Help me!
Consider the characteristics of water.
Pour it into a container, and it's square.
Pour it into a bottle, and it's round.
It can smash boulders or flow as far as the eye can see.
Of course. That's right!
I remember. There are ten water breathing forms,
so I can adapt to any opponent.
If you're wounded, then you have to
make a move that will compensate for it.
I can take on any form, and
this flow will never be stopped!
More important than my bones, my spirit was broken.
That's not gonna do anyone any good!
Would you stay out of my head, please?!
Look straight ahead.
Steel yourself.
Give it everything you've got.
You can do it!
I've been able to survive this long.
I know I have what it takes!
Whether it's today or tomorrow,
I can assure you this!
Without a shadow of doubt in my mind, I will not yield!