Were you acquainted with any of these demon slayers?
There don't seem to be any
survivors in this area, at least.
We were informed that several of the newer mizunoto
had joined the battle to combat these demons, but...
They might all be dead by now, don't you think?
Let's go.
Isn't the moon lovely?
Since we've been given this joint mission,
let's try to get along, Tomioka.
My only concern is slaying demons.
How coldhearted of you.
Well, how about we split up from this point?
I shall proceed from the west.
Very well.
Huh?
Don't you come near my family!
Stay away from them!
Water breathing. Second form,
water wheel!
It's no good.
It won't cut through.
Its body is so tough!
None of my techniques worked.
This is bad. What do I do?
I'll say it again so you understand.
Stay away from my family!
Hey, you! Eyes over here!
All nine of 'em!
Raah!
Damn it!
All that force with just a single swipe of its arm!
I can't beat him in my condition.
All this blood loss is making me dizzy.
Damn it!
Water breathing. Second form, improved,
lateral water wheel!
What happened?
What's going on here?
Inosuke! You all right?
Huh?
Wait. He did that?
What a little showoff.
Okay. I should be able to cut off its head now.
Water breathing,
the final and most powerful form!
He's got a different air about him now.
I can tell he's about to do
something that's totally incredible.
Now I'll finish him off!
Total concentration.
Water breathing.
Tenth form...
Hey, look out!
Kentaro!
Inosuke!
You have to hold on 'til I can make it back!
That's one of the Twelve Kizuki,
so you can't die here! You hear me?!
Promise me that you won't die!
Oh, crap!
It's starting to get...
Really hard to breathe now.
Not only that,
I don't have any feeling in my...
Arms and legs anymore.
Nezuko, I'm sorry.
Don't give up.
You hear me?
Don't give up!
Who is this?
Hello there.
Are you all right?
Water breathing. Second form...
Water wheel!
Somehow, I stuck that landing.
I beg of you, please stop!
What are you looking at?
This isn't a play, you know.
Wh-what are you doing?
Aren't you two fighting on the same side?
"The same side"?
Don't go phrasing it in such an infantile manner.
The two of us are family.
We are connected by a powerful bond.
Regardless of that, this is between me and my sister.
If you insist on interfering, I'll carve you up.
You're wrong.
Family or comrade, as long as
you feel close to one another,
that's all that really matters.
Saying it's childish if you're not related by blood,
that's not true at all!
Not only that,
but those who are strongly connected with each other
give off the scent of trust.
But all I'm picking up from you two
is the scent of terror, hatred, and revulsion!
That's not something you can call a bond!
It's a fake, a forgery!
You little...
Well, would you look at that!
A demon that's a manageable size.
Even I can deal with a kid.
This is my chance.
Hold on a second, please!
Don't move in on my prey!
This is how I'll secure my path up the ladder,
and with more status, comes more
money in my pockets from on high.
Even with most of my unit wiped out, I'll dispose of him,
and afterwards I'll descend the mountain
to claim my prize for defeating this demon.
Take this!
No, wait! Don't do it!
Cut to pieces in an instant.
How did he do that?
Now, then, what did you just say?
I asked you...
What did you say to me?
Look how scary he got.
It feels like the air became ten times heavier.
Inosuke, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna need you to hang in there a little longer.
I'll be there as soon as I defeat this demon.
I'll come help you, no matter what!
Answer me. What did you mean?
I demand to hear it from you.
Come now. Explain it to me.
Sure! I'd be happy to.
What you have isn't a real bond at all!
Not good.
Damn it. Hiding away like a woodland creature,
how pathetic is that?
I've gotta find a way to turn things around.
How do you cut someone who's swordproof, anyway?
What should I do? What can I do?
What's the way for me to get in there and hurt it?
Think! Think! Think!
Think...
Whoa!
This is bad! This is really bad!
Until... until he gets back,
I gotta survive somehow.
Why the hell am I thinkin' things like that?!
I don't have time for this!
Damn you.
I must have gotten infected by tontaro's germs!
I can't let my guard down again!
Using my head?
That kind of thing's not like me at all!
All right. I got you.
See? It was as simple as that.
If you can't cut something with a sword,
all you gotta do is pound on it with another sword!
And just my luck. I have the tools for the job!
I am untouchable!
Eh?
Are you running away on me?
Hey, you, come back here, damn it!
Just so you know,
I'm not going to kill you in a single strike.
Instead, I'll dissect you piece by piece.
However, if you take back what you said to me just now,
I'll make your death mercifully quick.
I refuse!
What I said was the unbridled truth!
I won't take it back, not on your life!
You're the one who's in the wrong!
Damn it. Where the hell did that abomination make off to?
It's just a scratch.
This doesn't hurt at all,
and if it doesn't hurt, it's not a problem!
I've had enough of this.
Time to sniff him out for good.
So there you are!
You dung-brained buffoon!
How high did you climb?
Bastard.
You're gonna try and force me to use my head again, huh?
I don't think so.
What the...
Oh, I get it!
He's trembling with fear and
dread at the mere sight of me, huh?
Well, it's a bit too late for that!
The hell?
Now what?
Did... did it just shed its skin?!
Give me a break.
I'm all about getting really strong,
but this is too much!
This is looking really bad.
I've never felt this much force from an opponent before.
A single strike will pulverize me.
It's hopeless. I can't win.
I'm gonna die.
This is the end.
Don't die!
Huh?
You have to hold on 'til I can make it back!
Always live your lives in a fashion where
you are able to hold your heads up high.
I wish you luck in battle.
I won't lose.
No way am I gonna lose.
I'm Inosuke Hashibira of the demon slayer corps!
Give me the worst you got, you dirtbag!
So fast. I can't even see it!
Beast breathing. Fang three,
devour!
It broke?
Damn it. I should have focused more on
my landing than my breathing technique.
I'll make sure you can never harm my family again!
I refuse to die here.
Beast breathing. Fang one.
All right, you brute. Take this!
I dug 'em in, but...
It's like it doesn't even matter.
This thing isn't even flinching!
Forgive me.
Please forgive me, Inosuke.
This way, at least you will have a chance.
Survive!
Who...
who are you?
What was that?
Did he actually cut through him?
Who... who could have possibly done such a thing?
So quick.
Water breathing. Fourth form...
Striking tide.
A-amazing.
I've... I've never seen anyone as incredible as this guy.
Good. The stench is starting to fade, so now
I'm able to detect the scent of the threads.
I can take him on now.
Hmph. He's smarter than I gave him credit for.
He doesn't shrink back in fear.
Not that any of that will matter in the end.
Water breathing. First form...
Water surface slash!