Nezuko!
No, don't chase him! Get back here!
Come to me.
No, Nezuko!
This is what Urokodaki was talking about.
Nezuko's a demon now.
She's not a weakling.
She doesn't need me to protect her.
She can handle herself.
So maybe she can handle this.
If she can protect these two, I can focus on my attack.
Nezuko!
Nezuko, I'm going underground!
Keep them safe for me.
Can you do that?
It's a swamp.
What are those?
It's clothing and stuff that
belonged to the people who were taken.
So many innocent victims, all murdered.
It's unforgivable.
Unforgivable!
Getting hard to breathe yet?
There isn't a whole lot of air down here in the swamp.
Also, the darkness closing in on
you only adds to the weight you feel.
You can't move the way you would above ground down here.
You should've looked before you leapt, you stupid fool!
You underestimate me.
After all, where do you think I got my training?
The air's even thinner up on
mount Sagiri than it is down here!
Besides...
Some moves only unleash their full potential underwater!
Guess it goes both ways.
They move even faster here!
But it doesn't matter.
All I have to do is slash when they get close enough.
I'll use the form that works
even when I don't have sure footing.
A quick and violent twist of my entire body,
generating a powerful vortex!
I've got the scent, the opening thread!
Total concentration!
Water breathing!
Sixth form!
Whirlpool!
Can't breathe.
I gotta get out of here!
Hurry!
This girl's powerful!
Seems like she hasn't picked up any skills yet,
but she's still so strong.
He must have given her a massive amount of blood.
She's so fast, I can't get back down to the swamp.
At least I'm starting to pick up the
pattern in all her one-note attacks.
It doesn't matter if she can kick my head off
or if my organs explode.
Demons can regenerate in no time!
That's right.
Now I'm gonna drill a hole right through your face!
Hands off my sister!
H-he just took me out?
This stupid kid beat two of me already?!
You smell horrible. You give off a scent like rotten oil.
I know where it comes from.
Tell me, how many people have you killed?
Give me a break already!
If women live too long, they turn ugly,
and then they won't taste good anymore!
I killed 'em for their own good!
You know, you should be thanking u...
Never mind.
Huh?
What do you know about Muzan Kibutsuji? Tell me!
Talk to me!
Come on! Talk!
I-I can't.
I-I can't tell you.
I can't do it.
I just can't.
You mustn't tell a soul.
No one can know anything about me.
Do you understand?
Don't forget. I'm always watching you,
so if you tell anyone, I will know about it.
I can't say! I can't!
I can't! I can't!
I can't!
Now the only thing I smell is fear.
He's terrified!
I can't tell you, all right?!
I failed to get any information again.
Nezuko!
She's asleep, and the bleeding stopped.
So that does help her recover.
I failed. I'm sorry.
But just hang on.
I promise you this, I will make you human again.
Mr. Kazumi...
Are you all right?
I lost my fiance.
How could I be all right?
Mr. Kazumi...
You have to go on, no matter what,
in spite of losing people...
Even though it's devastating.
How am I supposed to do that?!
You're just a kid! What do you know?!
I'll be on my way now.
Here.
Hopefully you'll find something of miss Satoko's in there.
You've been through this yourself, haven't you?
I-I'm sorry!
I shouldn't have said that! Please forgive me!
I'm so sorry!
His hands are heartbreaking,
hardened and thick from training.
They're not the hands of a boy.
I'm leaving the girl with you.
Get her home safe!
I'll do that!
I promise.
I'm not alone.
How many people have you killed?
Tortured? Tormented?
I'll never forgive you, Muzan Kibutsuji.
I'll make you pay.
Head to Asakusa, Tokyo now!
Rumor has it a demon's lurking around there!
Caw!
I've got another mission already?
Oh, yes, you do!
Could you at least give me a minute?
No time. Move it!
Come on. Just give me a chance to...
Just shut up, and get a move on!
Hey, knock it off!
The big cities have come a lot further than I expected.
It's nighttime, but it's so bright out.
The buildings are so tall!
What's the deal?!
Incredible and overwhelming.
This is making me dizzy.
Uh, let's go this way.
So sorry to bother you.
Pardon me, sir.
Huh?
Could I get a bowl of udon with grated yam?
Why, yes. Coming right up.
I've never been to a place like this before.
It's way too crowded.
Here's your udon with yam.
Let me know how you like it.
Oh, thank you very much.
That scent! Why is it here, and why now?!
It's the same scent I found at my house!
Muzan Kibutsuji.
it must be him! He's here!
Huh?
I found him.
Daddy?
Who's that?
He's...
What is this?
Is he...
he's living here, posing as a human!
I'm sorry. Is there something I can do for you?
Are you all right?
You seem to be a bit flustered.
Darling, what's the matter?
Don't worry, mother.
They're human.
The girl and the woman,
their scent is human.
But how?
Can't you tell?
This guy is a demon.
He eats people!
Who is this boy?
I really don't know.
I'm just as confused as you are.
I've never seen him before.
He must have made a mistake,
thought that I was someone else.
Oh, you think that's it?
Oh?
What's going on?
Are you all right, sweetheart?
You look pale.
No! Stop!