There's a reason I won,
because I learned how to detect the opening thread.
As soon as I pick up the scent,
I'm able to see the thread.
It guides me.
It connects my blade to any opening the enemy leaves me,
and it tightens as soon as I see it.
It quickly draws my blade forward.
Then I strike.
Urokodaki.
To be honest, I never had any intention
of sending you to the final selection.
Because I didn't want to see any more children die.
I was sure you wouldn't be able
to cut through this boulder, but...
Well done, Tanjiro.
Truly remarkable.
I'm very proud.
Make sure you come back from final selection alive.
Your sister and I will be waiting for you.
There's so much food. What's the deal?
You finished your training, so we're celebrating.
Time to eat. Don't be shy.
Thank you. I'm starving.
Tanjiro
I'm afraid there's nothing more I can do for you.
After today, you will be facing unimaginable hardships.
Your training pales in comparison.
But, at least for tonight,
you can rest well and sleep soundly one last time.
Hey, Tanjiro.
Eh? Yes?
What did you think of the hot pot?
Great! I haven't feasted like that in a while.
A growing boy with an appetite like yours will
get bigger and stronger, the bigger his meals are.
The same applies to demons.
Remember that.
The more humans a demon has
eaten, the more powerful he'll be.
So, if they eat a lot, they'll be tough to defeat?
That's right.
They get stronger, physical traits change,
and some learn to use strange spells.
You'll be able to tell how many poor souls they've claimed
once your sense of smell is even more developed.
What's this?
It is called a warding mask.
It's been enchanted by a protection spell
to keep you from harm.
Now it makes sense.
Nezuko.
I promise. I'm going to come back for you.
No need to worry about your sister.
I'll take good care of her for you.
Thanks for everything.
Guess I'm off. See you later!
Say hi to Sabito and Makomo!
Tanjiro? That's impossible.
How does he know the names of the dead?
Wisteria.
It's all over the place.
I thought it was out of season.
So many people.
Good evening.
Tonight you've come to enter the
demon slayer corps's final selection.
Thank you all for being here.
Here on mount Fujikasane,
there are several demons that were
captured alive by demon slayer swordsmen.
They are kept here for this event.
The Wisteria blossoms prevent them from leaving.
They bloom on this mountain year-round,
and they cover everything from
the base to halfway to the top.
But the Wisteria ends here,
so demons abound from this point on,
and they're very hungry.
In order to complete final selection,
you must survive for seven days
beyond the Wisteria's protection.
Now your trial begins.
Survive.
Don't think about anything else.
I just have to make it through the night.
Once the sun comes up, the
demons won't be able to do anything.
That'll be my chance to rest.
Which means I need to head east,
make my way to where the sunlight will hit first.
I smell a demon close by.
Where is it? Where's it coming from?
I can't seem to pin it down.
Up there!
Found you.
Damn you!
Why don't you go find your own snack?
This is my turf!
Your turf? Ah, go to hell!
Two already.
Can I handle them?
Says who?
I saw him first!
Doesn't matter! I'll be the first to kill him!
You've got this. Calm down, and watch closely.
Don't forget your training.
Haven't tasted human flesh in forever!
Total concentration.
Water breathing!
I smell the thread.
Fourth form!
Striking tide!
I did it.
I killed demons.
I'm getting stronger!
So my training wasn't for nothing.
I did master it.
Nothing's left behind when a
demon's killed with this sword,
not even the bones.
A demon's weakest at the neck.
However, a normal sword is useless, even upon the neck.
Okay. So how do I kill them?
With a demon slayer's katana
forged by a special type of steel.
That's the only weapon that can kill a demon.
It's called a nichirin sword.
Rest in peace.
What the...
What's that awful smell?
What the hell?!
I didn't sign up for this!
What?
My god. What is that?
Hey, Sabito.
You think Tanjiro can beat him?
I don't know.
It seems nothing's ever going to be enough.
You saw for yourself, didn't you?
What's this mutated demon doing here?
Nobody said anything!
Swallowed whole!
No!
Stay strong!
Save him. Save him. Save him.
You're not powerless anymore!
Move it!
Water breathing, second form!
Water wheel!
Well, look at that.
It's another one of those sweet little foxes.
"Another"?
Say, fox cub, the year?
Are we still in Meiji?
It's the Taisho period!
Taisho?
Already?!
We have passed into a new period?!
Again!
And I'm still stuck inside this Wisteria prison!
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Damn you, Urokodaki!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
You know Urokodaki?
Of course I do.
Urokodaki's the one who captured me and brought me here!
But that was 47 years ago now,
back when he was still hunting demons like me,
the Edo period, during the Keio era.
No way. Edo period?
You lie!
No demon could ever live that long in here!
Besides, all these demons have
only eaten two or three humans!
They die during final selection.
In fact, they even eat their own kind!
And yet I've managed to survive here all this time,
trapped in this flowery cage.
I've managed to devour at least 50 of you brats.
50 people?!
13.
That means you're number 14.
What are you talking about?
That's how many of Urokodaki's students I've eaten.
I promised myself I'd kill every single one of them.
You know, the ones who stood
out to me the most were those two.
Ah, yes.
The boy's hair was an unusual shade of pink,
a scar by his mouth.
He was the most powerful of the lot.
The other one was a girl who wore a flowery kimono,
small, not much power, but awfully agile.
So they were dead?
Killed by this demon?
But I was with them.
Your mask, that's what gives you
away as one of Urokodaki's brats.
Easy to spot the texture of one of the masks he's carved.
They always match the style of the tengu mask he wears.
He calls them "warding masks," right?
Except that's how I pick out who to eat.
They're all inside my belly.
It's as if he's guided them to their deaths.
When I told the girl,
she started crying and fell into a rage.
But it wasn't long before she
lost all control of her movement.
I ripped her limb from limb and feasted!
Calm down, Tanjiro.
Your breathing is uneven.
Stay focused. Forget about us.
You're on your own, buddy.
I'm getting out of here.
There goes another one of Urokodaki's brats.
I wonder, how will he feel when another
one of his children doesn't make it back home?
Oh, I wish I could see the look on his face.
I bet it's going to be priceless.
If only I could be there.
Tanjiro!
What's this? He can still move.
That means I can have some fun!
Damn! I can't just cut his arms off.
They regrow too fast!
That's not going to be enough
for you to beat me, little fox.
But, then again, not even that
pink-haired brat could cut off my head!
There's no way I can just let him go.
I won't let another life be sacrificed.
No more! I'll take him down!
Wait a second. Underground!
H-he jumped!
Damn it, how did he know?
No matter. He won't be able to dodge an attack in midair!
Do you think he's going to beat Tanjiro, too?
His neck is thick. Can it be cut?
I can't say whether he'll win or lose today.
However, one fact is irrefutable either way.
Tanjiro cut through this boulder,
the toughest and largest boulder of them all.
He deflected it!
Total concentration. Water breathing!
I let him get too close.
Not to worry. My neck is tough. He can't cut through it.
First form!
As soon as he fails, I'm going
to grab his head and crush it,
just like I did to the other one!
Water surface slash!