Incredible.
Look at 'em go.
That's it!
You really are fast, Kanao.
Your score is now ten wins and ten loses.
I'm still up for more.
Let's go for a run.
Wanna join me?
Doing total concentration, constant?
Yeah.
I gotta keep this up?
Do me next!
How's this?
That's nothin'!
More brawn than brain.
Let's go!
Where the hell is this place?
Is this her blood demon art?
It looks like the whole space
is distorted around that woman.
Only the lower ranks of the
Twelve Kizuki have been summoned.
That's never happened before.
Lower five isn't here yet.
It moved! Is this her doing?
what is it with this woman?
Who is she?
Lower your heads, and kneel down.
Prostrate yourselves.
That's Master Muzan's voice.
I didn't recognize him at all!
Even his aura is completely different.
His disguise is astounding.
Please forgive us, Master!
Since you've assumed a different form, we...
Who gave you permission to speak?
Don't presume your thoughts are of any worth to me.
All you are allowed to do is answer my questions.
The lower five was killed.
His name was Rui.
This is my single question for all of you.
Why is it you demons in the
lower ranks are so utterly weak?
You shouldn't be satisfied merely
being among the Twelve Kizuki.
That is only the start.
You must devour more humans, gain more power.
That is the path to becoming useful to me.
For over a century,
the upper members of the Twelve
Kizuki have remained unchanged,
and it has always been those members
who have disposed of the Hashira.
Meanwhile, how many times have you been replaced?
You make it sound so easy,
but the fact is...
"You make it sound so easy,
but the fact is..."
What? Say it.
He can read my mind?
This is bad.
What is bad?
Finish your thought.
Forgive me, Master Kibutsuji!
Please! Please show me mercy!
I'm sorry! I'm so very, very sorry!
Why is this happening?
Am I next?
After all I went through to become a Twelve Kizuki,
why? Why this?
I thought I was going to do so much more!
Are you more afraid of the demon slayers than of me?
No!
I'm sure every time you run
into a Hashira-level Demon Slayer,
your only thoughts are of escaping.
No, I'd never do that!
I would put my own life on the
line in order to fight for you!
You're not contradicting what I just said, are you?
It's all hopeless.
Whether we agree or disagree with him,
he's going to kill us.
We can't beat him in a fight, either.
In that case...
I'll run!
What a fool.
I just need to make it out of here somehow.
Now that I'm far away...
The Twelve Kizuki are better off
consisting of just the upper ranks.
I will be dismantling the others.
He got me?
How?
Was it that fute player's technique?
No, I didn't hear it make any sounds.
I can't regenerate my body. Why?
Do either of you have any last words to share?
I can still be of use to you!
If you could just give me a little
bit of time, I swear you won't regret it!
Exactly how long are you asking for?
How do you intend to be useful to me,
and what precisely can you
accomplish with your meager skills?
Your blood!
If you could give me a portion of your blood,
I will surely rise to meet your expectations!
I will fight for you stronger than before!
Do you actually believe you're in any
position to order me to give you my blood?
Shameless is an understatement.
You will remember your place.
You misunderstand me!
I only said...
Silence. I misunderstood nothing.
I am never mistaken.
I am the one who calls the shots.
My word is absolute.
What I say is correct by default.
It is not for you to refute.
And yet you try to give me instructions?
You deserve to die for that.
Do you have any last words?
He'll be next to go.
Everything hinges on the Master's mood.
I'll be dead soon myself.
Well, let me see.
This is all like a wonderful dream for me.
For me to be able to perish
by your very hand in the flesh.
And I so enjoyed hearing the other demons's dying breaths.
How truly fortunate am I.
I do so love to see others in
the throes of despair and agony.
It's like a dream come true for me.
You have my profound gratitude for saving me for the end.
That's more like it.
I'll give you a generous amount of my blood,
although you may not be able
to handle its magnitude and die.
If you do manage to acclimate,
you are certain to become stronger.
Then you are to make yourself useful...
By killing Hashira of the demon slayers.
If you are able to kill the Demon
Slayer wearing hanafuda earrings,
I will give you even more of my blood.
What's this?
I see something.
It's pouring into me along with Master Muzan's blood.
If I kill a Hashira and this
kid, I can get even more blood.
It's like a dream.
It is now morning!
Wake up, everyone!
The hell?
Uh, what's going on?
The casualties of the mugen train...
more than 40 are missing as it currently stands.
You are to join Kyojuro Rengoku on-site.
Head west at once! Head west at once!
For the Mugen Train mission,
I've decided to send Tanjiro and the others.
Might I ask what caused you to
recommend him in the first place, Shinobu?
Tanjiro has a pure soul and will
work diligently toward all his goals,
and the potential he showed exceeded my expectations.
And perhaps most importantly of all,
he has a clear path in mind in
regards to defeating Kibutsuji.
I am in complete agreement with you on those counts.
On another matter,
Tanjiro told me that his father had used fire breathing.
Ah.
As of now, there's no denying
that he still has quite a way to go,
but I think that Rengoku, our flame
Hashira, could give him assistance.
Fair enough.
Considering that his sister is not a danger to humans,
as well as the fact he came face to face with Muzan,
these signs may very well point
towards this being Tanjiro's destiny.
All right, it's time to go!
Hmm? Someone's coming.
He was really intent on bumping into me.
Wait. This guy...
Was he at final selection?
he bulked up a lot in such a short time...
But there's something else...
His scent.
It's been awhile!
Glad to see you're doing well!
Oh, really?
You're heading out now?
It was only for a short time, but
I'm glad we got to spend it together.
Good luck out there.
You take care now.
Thanks for everything. You looked after us,
even though you were busy yourself,
and now we can get back into battle.
No need to thank me.
It was by chance I got through final selection,
and after that, I was too cowardly
to even step foot into battle.
None of that matters.
Because you kindly helped me out, aoi,
you're a part of me now.
All your emotions, I'll carry them into the battlefield.
If I get hurt, I hope you'll look after me again!
There you are!
Hey, Kanao!
We're heading out now.
Thanks for everything.
Uh...
Hmm? What's that?
All I did was follow the teacher's orders,
and so there's no need for you to thank me.
Farewell.
She actually talked to me!
What was that you just flipped?
Bye for now.
Money?
It says "heads" and "tails," huh?
Why did you flip it?
Goodbye.
You sure made that thing spin.
I flip this to help me decide things that weren't ordered.
Just now, I decided whether to speak to you or not.
Don't speak was heads, and do speak
was tails, and tails is what it landed on.
Farewell.
Why don't you choose for yourself?
Which do you wanna do?
It doesn't matter.
Nothing matters to me, so I can't decide for myself.
I don't think there's anything
in this world that doesn't matter.
I guess...
The voice in your heart is just really tiny.
Following orders is important to an extent, but...
Hey, can I borrow that?
Uh, sure.
Thank you.
Okay, we're gonna use this to decide!
Decide?
Whether you'll listen to your own heart
from this point on!
Whoa!
I flipped it way too high!
Heads! Let's make it heads!
If it comes up as heads, you're
going to follow your heart!
Huh? Hey!
Where did it go?
Oh, is that it?
You see that, Kanao? I got it!
Are you ready?
Which will it be?
His back was blocking it, so I
couldn't see which way it fell.
It came up as heads!
Here you go!
remember...
It's the heart that drives people,
so it can grow as strong as you need it to.
All right. See you later!
How... how did it come up heads?!
I saw his hand when he flipped it.
I'm sure he didn't cheat, but still...
Just by chance.
Although, if it were tails, I was gonna keep
tossing it until it finally came up as heads.
Take care of yourself!
You can do it! You can do it! You can do it!
Great job, everyone!
Here!
Ahh.
Thanks, girls.
Don't eat it now.
We hope you all defeat a lot of demons.
We'll do our best.
Hey, I told you not to eat it now!
Shut up!
Someone should teach you some manners!
Tomioka!
Heading into battle now?
Yes, sir.
I hear that you've mastered
total concentration, constant.
I have.
You should keep at it.
Yes, sir.
Tomioka...
About Nezuko...
Thank you very much.
The fact that you put your life on the line,
I had no idea.
I don't know how to ever repay you.
You can thank me by doing your best work.
Our mission is to kill demons.
That is all. Got it?
Got it!
Be safe, you guys.
Oh, no! Saying goodbye has broken your little hearts.
I can stay behind if you like.
Zenitsu, while you're on your journey,
please learn to be considerate
and respectful of girls, okay?
Yes.
I'm feeling happy.
You do feel a little sad that I'm leaving, though, right?
We're not sad!
All right, everyone!
We're heading out now!
Hey, wait a damn minute!
Wh-what the...
What the hell is this creature?!
Wait. Could it be?
I've heard of such a being,
the Master and ruler of this land!
At such an intimidating size,
there's no mistaking it!
It looks like it's asleep, but don't let that fool you!
It's a train. You've never seen one?
Pipe down, or you'll wake it!
I'll lead the charge to take it down!
Inosuke, stop!
Huh?
This might be the guardian spirit of this land,
so we shouldn't be attacking it carelessly.
Uh, I said it's a train.
You've never seen one, either?
A vehicle for transportation?
Man, you're sheltered.
Huh? A train?
That's what the crow was talking about?
Eh?
Huh?
What is he doing?
Ready or not, I'm comin' through!
Stop embarrassing us!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
Look!
These three have swords!
The police! Call the police!
Not good! Not good! Not good!
Run for it!
We went through hell 'cause of
you, Inosuke! Say you're sorry!
Oh, yeah?! Explain to me why we had to
run from those guys in the first place?!
'Cause demon slayers aren't
officially recognized by the government,
so we can't just have our swords out in public like that.
If we told them about the demons,
it's not like they would believe us, anyway, you know?
But we're trying hard to help everyone.
It's the way things go.
For now, let's hide our swords away.
We can see them. Put something on.
Oh, no! The train's leaving!
Are the police still around?
We have to go, either way!
Hah hah!
Here I come, Master of the land!
What are you doing?!
We should go, too!
Hey! You three!
Tanjiro! Inosuke!
Zenitsu!
This thing's fast!
Hey, Tanjiro...
Eh?
You sure about bringing Nezuko along?
Wouldn't the safest place for her
be back at headquarters?
This is fine.
Wherever we go, we will always be together.
We're never going to be apart again.
No matter what it takes,
your big brother will save you!
Muzan Kibutsuji,
no matter where you go,
I promise you won't escape me!
Nezuko's staying with me.
Nothing's gonna break us apart.
The bond between Nezuko and I...
Cannot be severed...
Not by anyone!
Nezuko...
I swear to you...