I've been able to survive this
long. I know I have what it takes!
Whether it's today or tomorrow, I can assure you this!
Without a shadow of doubt in my mind, I will not yield!
Tanjiro, where are you right now?
I can still hear that creepy sound.
I just hope he's safe.
Um, Zenitsu, is it me, or are we
just going around and around in circles?
I knew it! I was getting the exact same feeling!
I knew I could rely on you to help me out, Shoichi!
All right. Can you check to see if this room is clear?
Hey, what's with that look?! All right,
all right, fine! You win! I'll do it myself!
There's nobody here. Let's go this way.
Where are you, Tanjiro? You can come out now!
Wait. Did this room just...
Flip over?!
I can do it. I know I can. I always finish what I start.
No matter what, even with my body in this
condition, I can pull through and keep fighting!
show him that a few broken bones isn't gonna slow me down!
Damn it! I can't win like this.
I need more than just determination.
Calm down. Use your head to think things through.
Think, Tanjiro! Think!
That was close. I barely scraped by there.
Curses! This is irritating. I need to
consume some Marechi before it's too late.
There's not even time to think!
Hey, you! What's your name?
It's Kyogai.
Kyogai! Listen, I'm not giving
you that child! I won't bend to you!
It's futile!
Don't you see that it's futile?
I will get my hands on that boy and reclaim
my rightful place among the Twelve Kizuki!
Don't you see that it's futile?
This is so boring!
Disappointing. Your writing is absolutely insipid.
Every last word on these pages is utterly trite!
There's no beauty, vulnerability, or impact.
Why don't you forget this fantasy of being a
writer? It would simply be a waste of ink and paper.
It doesn't help that you never even step outside
anymore. It's no wonder you're such a dull individual.
And, if that's the case, you might as well
stick with your original hobby of playing the drum.
Not that you're good enough to be
more than an amateur with that, either.
Damn insect! Get out of my sight!
Rapid drumming!
Don't tell me he can strike that drum even faster!
The speed of these rotations is making me
dizzy! This is bad. What a terrifying skill.
Not only that, but now he's
using five claws instead of three!
I got it!
Now that I've dodged his strikes
without stepping on those papers,
I can protect my wounds, because I
know how to move around and breathe.
Take quick, shallow breaths.
Use that breathing technique to reinforce
the muscles around your broken leg!
Also, right before the claw attack,
there's a strong scent of mold.
I smell it! Here it comes!
from above!
Left!
Right!
From behind!
He's evading all of my attacks.
Total concentration. Water breathing.
Ninth form, splashing water flow, turbulent!
Minimize the landing time and area as much as possible.
He's adapting to the changes of the room.
Go, Tanjiro. Get within striking distance.
Closer. Don't give him any room to breathe!
I see the opening thread.
Kyogai!
Your blood demon art was truly incredible!
I took a deep breath by mistake.
It's okay, Tanjiro, you can bear this. It'll pass!
Boy...
Answer me.
Did you really think my blood demon art... was incredible?
I truly did. However...
I can't forgive you for killing.
I see.
Oh, that's right. Gotta get a blood sample.
Wow, it worked.
He said it would automatically
extract blood when applied like this,
but seeing it in action proves
how crafty Yushiro really is.
A cat?
Oh! You're the one who's going to
deliver this to miss Tamayo, right?
Here we are. Good kitty!
You're all set!
All right. Take care!
I was told that, under Yushiro's spell,
it would be invisible until it meowed,
and then vanish again when it meowed a second time.
So it's true, then.
Those kids. I gotta find them!
My--my writing...
Disappointing. Your writing is absolutely insipid.
Every last word on these pages is utterly trite!
There's no beauty, vulnerability, or impact.
It wasn't worthless.
At the very least, that child didn't believe so.
He respectfully avoided trampling upon my work.
May your soul rest in peace.
Both my blood demon art and my drum playing...
Have been recognized.
Kiyoshi! Teruko! Are you here? Answer me!
Teruko! Kiyoshi!
Sorry, Tanjiro.
Why are the two of you throwing stuff at me?
We're sorry. The drum we were
using disappeared, so we panicked.
I see. Well, you're safe. I'm glad.
You did a great job hanging in there. You,
too, Kiyoshi. Come on. Let's head outside.
Kiyoshi, hop on.
How's your leg feeling?
Not too bad.
Just hang on a little longer.
I'm picking up Zenitsu and Shoichi's
scent. They're probably outside.
Seems they're both sa...
I smell blood.
What's the matter?
Nothing. Let's hurry along.
Take this! Come on! Move it!
Now, you spineless coward! Draw your sword, and face me!
Tanjiro...
The box, I protected it.
You told me... This was more
important to you than your own life.
That's why I did it.
The fact is, I've always had really good hearing.
There have been times when I knew what
people said, even though I had been fast asleep.
That really creeped everyone out.
I don't hear any more demons. You
must have finished the job, Tanjiro.
I can hear you all and also
these odd-sounding, loud footsteps.
Zenitsu! Zenitsu! Please, wake up!
Oh. Thank goodness! Are you all right?
When the room spun around earlier,
we ended up getting thrown outside.
We fell from the second-story window.
Did we, really?
Yeah, you made sure that I was protected at the
time, though, so I didn't end up getting hurt at all.
I'm glad to hear that. So what's with all the tears, then?
Now I understand! I fell right onto my head, didn't I?!
Yes.
Am I gonna... am I gonna die?!
Oh, no. The world is starting
to spin. Is this the end for me?!
What's going on? I don't like that sound!
Watch out, 'cause, ready or not, I'm comin' through!
There it is again, that terrifying boar monster!
Picking up a demonic presence here.
Hey, wait. I know where I've heard that
voice before. He's the fifth survivor.
During final selection, he was the first to rush
up the mountain and the first to come back down.
What a force of nature!
Hmm?
I've found you, demon!
Stop it!
What the hell? Who are you? Get outta my way!
My name is Zenitsu Agatsuma! I'm
a demon slayer, the same as you!
Oh? Are you, now?
Then, you should already know! We
gotta get rid of that thing at all costs!
Now get the hell out of my way!
I refuse! This belongs to Tanjiro...
Don't you argue with me!
I'll deal with him and his box if that's
the case. I won't say it again. Move!
Do you wanna die?
This box, I won't let you touch it!
I don't know what's inside, but I
know that it's precious to Tanjiro!
Are you serious? Use your damn head!
There's a demon in that box! Don't you get that?
Of course I do! I've known that from the very start!
I knew he was traveling with a demon,
because the sounds demons make
aren't anything like a human.
That said, the sounds I hear from Tanjiro
are so kind and gentle, it makes me want to cry.
I don't think I've ever heard anything like it before.
All living creatures constantly give off
vibrations. The world is full of sounds ringing out...
Breathing, heartbeats, the rhythm of blood circulating.
By listening closely, I'm able to tell what
kind of thoughts are going through someone's head.
Even so, I've been deceived by others many times.
That's because I've always stubbornly
believed in whomever I wanted.
Tanjiro, despite being a demon
slayer, is traveling with a demon,
but I'm sure he has a good reason for doing so.
Whatever that reason may be, I'm
sure I can put my faith behind it.
I'll do it.
I'll ask him. I'll ask Tanjiro about the demon
myself. Until that happens, just leave it alone!
Let go of me, damn it!
You're a pest!
I won't let you touch that!
It's important to Tanjiro. Stay away from it!
You're not laying a finger on it until he gets back!
Damn you!
Take this!
Move it!
No! I refuse!
Take this! Come on! Move it!
Now, you spineless coward! Draw your sword, and face me!
Tanjiro...
The box, I protected it.
You told me. This was more
important to you than your own life.
That's why I did it.
You idiot! After all that bluster,
you don't even bother to draw your sword!
If you're a fellow demon slayer, then let's see you fight!
If you're not gonna fight,
then get the hell out of my way!
Move aside!
Fine, then. If all you're gonna
do is keep me from doing my job,
then you leave no choice, but to
take you out along with that box!
Stop it!
I said stop!