Wake up. I said wake up! You gotta...
Hey, can you even hear me? Come on! Get up!
Are you gonna sleep all day? Wake the hell up, will you?!
I heard he was a Demon Slayer with a demon in tow,
so I was expecting someone with more flair.
But it's just some ordinary-looking kid? Too bad.
We must see that this boy is put on trial to be judged.
So it shall be!
To think that he's been protecting his sister, who's now a
demon, what a brave and beautiful display of sibling love!
What... who are these people...
Don't open your mouth until you're told! Do you know
who you're in the presence of? These are the Hashira!
The Hashira? What is that? I have no idea.
Who are all these people?
Where even am I?
This is the demon slayers's headquarters. You are
here because you, Tanjiro Kamado, are to be put on trial.
Before we begin the trial, why don't you
explain the crime you have been accused of...
There's no need for a trial!
Protecting a demon is a clear violation! We can
deal with this on our own! We shall execute them both!
In that case, I'll
decapitate them with style.
I'll show you the most dramatic spray
of blood ever! It'll be a spectacle.
No way! You'd really kill such an adorable child as him?
Such a thought fills my heart with sorrow.
Alas, to see such a pitiful creature as this.
I grieve for him.
Perhaps it would have been better if he hadn't been born.
Um, what was the shape of that cloud again?
What was it called?
Wait. Where's Nezuko?
Hey, you. The Hashira are speaking. What are
you looking at? Your eyes should be over there.
These are the nine highest-ranking swordsmen
in the Demon Slayer Corps.
That's the Hashira?
Let's end his misery.
Right!
And let's do so with flair.
Hey!
Nezuko! Where did you take her?
Nezuko! Zenitsu! Inosuke! Murata!
Never mind this boy. What will we do with Tomioka?
Seeing him standing there
without any restraints is making me feel ill.
Based on what Kocho told us,
he's just as guilty of breaking the Corps rules.
How should we make him take responsibility?
What kind of lesson shall we teach him?
What do you have to say for yourself, Tomioka?
He's in this situation because of me.
Iguro, you're as sharp tongued as ever, I see.
I love that side of you!
Tomioka's all by himself, all stoic-like. What a cutie!
Oh, I think it's fine. He did come here without resisting.
Let's come up with a penalty later.
What I'm more interested in is hearing this boy's story.
He's been traveling with a demon alongside him,
despite being a Demon Slayer himself.
I wish to hear why
and hear it straight from the boy's mouth.
What he's done is unquestionably
against the Demon Slayer Corps rules.
You are aware of that, aren't you?
Tanjiro Kamado, why are you traveling
with a demon, as a fellow Demon Slayer?
Who cares why?
You can take your time. Just answer the question.
She's my... She's my young...
It looks like you need some water.
I can tell you've injured your jaw, so please drink
slowly. I added an anesthetic to the water to help.
Your wounds are still healing,
so you shouldn't push yourself too much.
Are you ready to tell us your story, Tanjiro?
That demon is my little sister! My family was attacked
by a demon while I was gone, and I lost almost everyone!
My sister was turned into a demon, but she's
never hurt anyone! She never has and never will!
She'll never harm a human being, no matter what!
Enough. Spare us these absurd ramblings.
If she's family, it's no wonder you're defending her.
I can't trust a single word you're spouting.
I don't believe you for a moment.
So sad. He's been possessed by a demon.
Let us end this child's life
and free him from this cursed existence!
Please listen to me!
I became a swordsman in hopes of finding a cure for her!
It has been two whole years since Nezuko became a demon!
She's never devoured anyone in that time!
Your storytelling is lacking any vibrant sparks of color.
"She hasn't devoured anyone, and she's not going to."
If you're gonna plead your
case, at least spice it up a bit!
What's that bird called again?
Was it...
Excuse me.
Something about this concerns me.
I find it hard to believe the Master
would have been unaware of this situation.
I don't think we should act without his permission.
Maybe it's best if we wait until he arrives.
My sister! Let my sister fight by my side!
I know she can fight as a Demon
Slayer to protect humans, so please...
Well, well, what kind of fun do we have brewing here?
Is that the moron who brought a demon along with him?
What the hell do you think
you're trying to pull here, exactly?
Those new scars
make Shinazugawa look even more handsome!
Please, Master Shinazugawa!
I must ask you to put down that box.
Wow! Even when she's angry,
Shinobu still looks as cool as ever.
Shinazugawa, please don't act out of line.
Run that by me again, kid?
"She can fight as a Demon Slayer to protect
humans." Was that it? You know what we call that?
Completely impossible, you idiot!
Anyone who harms my sister answers to me!
I don't give a damn if you're one of the Hashira!
Well, how very nice for you.
Cease this! The Master will be arriving shortly!
Pardon me.
Damn you.
Tomioka's outburst must have been a distraction,
but that boy still managed to get a blow in.
If you can't tell the difference between good
demons and bad ones, then you shouldn't be a Hashira!
You no-good, little I'll destroy you!
The Master of the mansion has returned.
My beloved children,
I thank you for coming here this day.
The Master of the mansion has returned.
Good morning to you all. The weather is
strikingly nice today. Perhaps with a blue sky?
Finding ourselves here at the semiannual
gathering with all the same faces, it brings me joy.
So this is the Master? He looks wounded. No, sick, maybe.
So quick! I couldn't even react! What is he?
I am pleased to see you in good health as well, Master.
I fervently pray for your continued good fortune.
I thank you, Sanemi.
I wanted to be the one to welcome the Master!
If I may, Master, before we start this meeting,
would you kindly enlighten us
about this young swordsman right here,
who it would appear has been accompanied by a demon?
He didn't seem to have any social graces before,
but now he's speaking so formally.
But of course. I apologize for any confusion.
Tanjiro and Nezuko have both been sanctioned.
I would appreciate it if you'd all accept this condition.
Master, even though it is something you have requested,
I cannot bring myself to do it.
I am also opposed to this!
A slayer traveling with a demon is unacceptable!
As for myself, I shall do whatever it is you wish, Master!
I'll forget, anyway... so I'm fine either way.
I won't trust them. Absolutely not.
First of all, I loathe demons.
Although I respect you with all my heart,
Master, I cannot abide by this! I'm fully against it!
The Corps's mission is to annihilate demons.
I ask that you punish Kamado and Tomioka!
The letter.
Yes, sir.
A former Hashira, Mr. Urokodaki,
sent along to us this letter with a request.
I shall read to you an abridged version.
"I ask you to allow Tanjiro and
his sister to accompany each other.
Because of her resilient mental fortitude"
Nezuko has not lost her human reason.
Even when starved, she has never devoured a human,
and that is true more than two years later.
Although the situation sounds outlandish,
it is in fact reality.
In the event that Nezuko does assault
another human being, myself, as well as.
"Tanjiro Kamado and Giyu Tomioka,
will atone by committing seppuku."
Who cares how they choose to end their lives?
Fire, hanging, it's all the same!
It doesn't guarantee our safety!
Shinazugawa is right! If she kills a human, we can't
turn back the clock. That person will be lost forever!
You do have a point.
So, then... What do you wish, Master?
We can't guarantee that she won't attack humans.
We can't prove it.
That said... We also cannot be
certain she will attack humans.
Here is what we do know about her for certain.
She has been abstinent for over two years, and there
are three people who would vouch for her with their lives.
If this evidence is rejected,
one must offer in turn an even more convincing argument.
Are any of you able to do so?
Also, there is another thing
I'd like to relay to you, my children.
Tanjiro has met Kibutsuji face to face.
That's impossible!
Not even a Hashira has ever crossed paths with him!
Did you, really? What did he look like?
What are his powers? Where did you see him?
Did you fight?
What was Kibutsuji doing?!
Did you find his stronghold?! Answer me!
Shut up! I asked him first!
Come on. Tell us what powers Kibutsuji has!
Speaking of that man,
we know he has sent pursuers after Tanjiro.
While his goal may simply be to silence Tanjiro,
now that he has finally revealed himself,
I wish to seize on this opportunity.
I also believe something is happening to Nezuko
that Kibutsuji never saw coming.
Do you agree with me now?
I'm afraid I don't, Master.
If it were human, there would be no question
we'd spare it, but after all we've gone through,
after losing countless of our brethren,
asking us to house a demon, it's unacceptable.
Wh-what is he doing? What is he doing?
Not all over the garden!
Hear me, Master! The depravity of a
demon, I will prove it to you, here and now!
Sanemi.
Hey, demon, it's time for your dinner. Take a bite.
No need to hold back. Just show us your true
colors, and then I'll destroy you right here.
Get away from her!
It's the daytime. No good doing this now.
It'll only show itself in the shadows.
Master, please forgive
the discourtesy I am about to commit.
Stop it!
Come on out, demon. It's the human blood you love so much!
I can't breathe. I can't move.
N-Nezuko.