Oh?
What's going on?
Are you all right, sweetheart?
You look pale.
No! Stop!
What is it?
What's wrong?
Is that blood?
Stop! No!
No! Sweetheart!
Listen!
You need to worry about yourself, ma'am!
Cover that wound, and apply as much pressure as you can!
It's all right. It'll all turn out fine.
The woman's wound doesn't look fatal.
Press down harder!
It needs more pressure! Tie it down with a rope!
It's gonna be okay.
This man hasn't killed anyone yet.
A few seconds ago, this guy was minding
his own business, walking down the street!
Are you all right?
Don't look, okay?
Rei, I think we should go. It's not safe.
Where is he?
Damn.
Damn it all!
I can't leave this man alone here.
Muzan Kibutsuji!
No matter where you go,
I promise you won't escape me!
What's the matter with that boy, Tsukihiko?
Tsukihiko?
You can run as far as you want!
I'll follow you to the ends of hell,
and my blade will be the last thing you see!
I'll never forgive you for what you've done!
What the hell's going on over here?
Another drunk.
Step away from that man right now, kid!
I can't!
Bring restraints to hold him down! Quickly!
Get away from him. Get up!
Please don't do that!
I'm the only one who can hold him back!
Get off!
I'm begging you, no!
Get a load of this guy's face.
Looks like he's lost his mind!
Help me get the kid off him!
Let me go! I don't want to let this person kill anybody!
Just stay out of the way! Someone could get hurt!
Damn it. Listen to me!
If you keep resisting, I'll have to use force.
Scent of illusory blood.
Visual dream.
That smell, what is it?
Huh? What's with the flowers?
The hell is this?! I can't see anything!
Some kind of spell?
That could mean trouble.
The smell's getting stronger.
I beg your pardon, but you said, "person,"
even though this particular person is now a demon,
and now you're trying to save him.
So, if you don't mind,
I'd like to lend you a hand.
Why in the world would you...
your scent. I know what you are.
You do. I'm a demon.
But I am also a doctor.
I want to help,
and I want to destroy Kibutsuji as well.
You're not coming with us, daddy?
No, daddy has work to do.
I have to go to a boring old business meeting,
and I'm worried about what just happened.
Oh, darling.
Not to worry.
I'm just going down to check in with the police.
Now hop in.
Promise you'll come home soon, okay, daddy?
I will. Be a good girl for mommy.
Take them back to the house.
Quickly, please.
Come on! Let's hit one more bar!
Are you feeling all right there?
Yeah, I'm fine!
I'm not even a little bit drunk yet... huh?
Hey, what the hell are you doing, mister?
Apologies.
Where you goin'?
I'm terribly sorry, but I'm in a bit of a hurry.
What the hell'd you say to me?
Look at you, all decked out in your fancy-pants clothes.
You're pissin' me off,
you and your stupid pale face.
You look like you're about to fall over dead.
aren't you gonna say anything, or did you just croak?
Hmm?
No!
What'd you do to my kid brother?
No! He's dead!
This monster killed him!
You bast...
So does my complexion look at all unhealthy to you?
Does my face seem unusually pale?
Do I look a bit sickly?
Does it appear I'm not long for this world?
Do you fear for my life?
You couldn't possibly be more wrong.
I'm very much alive and not far from perfection.
What do you think would happen if I
gave you a constant stream of my blood?
The human body is unable to
withstand such a rapid transformation.
And its cells are destroyed.
There's a demon slayer who wears hanafuda earrings.
I want you to bring me his head.
Got that?
Yes.
As you wish.
Hanafuda earrings.
As you would listen to me,
all right?!
It has nothing to do with money!
That's not the problem here!
I just can't forgive the fact that you would
walk away from a perfectly good bowl of udon!
I'm so sorry!
Can I please have another one?
To eat?
Yes!
You promise?
I promise!
All right.
What about you? If you're eating udon,
you better take off that bamboo
thingie! What the heck is it, anyway?
Now take these chopsticks, all right?!
I'd like a bowl of udon!
In fact, give me two of 'em!
Uh, okay.
Thanks for the great meal!
It was delicious!
I'm glad you liked it!
Come back again!
Anytime!
I'm so sorry, Nezuko.
I left you behind.
Eh?
What is it? What's wrong?
Are you out here waiting for us?
I'm here on her orders.
I'm supposed to bring you back with me.
You know, I could have just tracked your scent.
Our hiding place is protected by a concealment spell.
You'd never have found it.
Concealment?
Before we go,
did you know that girl is a demon?
And not much to look at.
What was that? Did he just...
doesn't that mean ugly?
But who...
Nezuko?!
You've gotta be out of your mind!
Who would look at Nezuko and think she's ugly?!
She was the most beautiful girl
in our whole town! You know that?!
Let's go.
I know!
We're already coming!
But take back what you said about her!
You just need to get a good look at her somewhere
with better lighting! Come on! Over there! Let's go!
I know what it is! It's this stupid muzzle!
That's the only explanation.
You just need to behold Nezuko's beauty
when she's not wearing this ugly thing!
Huh?
Hurry it up, while nobody's looking.
I could have sworn that street was a dead end.
Pay attention!
Now, make sure you don't offend the lady in any way,
because I couldn't care less what happens to you.
I only brought you here because she insisted. Got it?
Uh, okay, sure.
Come in.
I've returned, my lady.
I'm glad you made it.
I'm sorry that I left everything for
you to take care of. So how's she doing?
She'll make a full recovery.
But her husband has to be locked up.
He's restrained in the basement.
Isn't it difficult treating humans?
All of that blood...
Is that what you think,
she chokes back her own drool when she treats a human?
'Cause demons can't control themselves?
Sorry.
Don't do that.
Why would you resort to violence?
Did I ever introduce myself?
Apologies. My name is Tamayo,
and this is Yushiro.
I hope you two can be friends.
That seems unlikely.
It's not all that difficult,
at least, not for me,
but it's different for other demons.
My body's physiology has gone
through considerable changes,
and I've removed Kibutsuji's curse.
What curse?
And what kind of changes?
Come with me.
Hey, Nezuko, that's bad manners.
It's quite all right.
Make yourselves at home.
Sorry about that.
As I was saying, I made several adjustments
to our bodies so that we could continue to live
without harming any human beings.
We can survive on just a small amount of human blood.
Wait. Blood?
So you're saying...
I understand if you find it distasteful,
but I buy it from those in poverty.
I tell them I'll use it for transfusions.
But, of course, I never take
enough blood to impair anyone.
No wonder.
That would explain why neither one of
them has the same scent as a normal demon.
Except, they still need human blood.
If that's the case, what about Nezuko?
And Yushiro needs even less blood than I do,
since I'm the one who turned him into a demon.
Huh? You turned him?
But how?
How did I do it?
As far as anyone knows, Kibutsuji
is the only one who can create demons,
and that's more or less accurate.
It took me over 200 years, and, after
all that, I could only transform Yushiro.
Two...
200 years?
It took you 200 years before you could
figure out how to transform just one person?!
How old are you, miss Tamayo?!
You should know better than to ask a lady her age!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Yushiro, if you hit that boy
again, I'll make you regret it.
Yes, ma'am!
She's beautiful, even when she's angry.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to clarify that further.
Creating more demons is not one of my goals.
And I only do so when necessary,
the terminally ill or injured,
only when they won't survive.
And, even in those cases, I always ask in
advance if they truly prefer to live on as a demon.
Her scent is pure. No sign of deception.
I think I can trust her.
Miss Tamayo...
Once someone becomes a demon,
is there a way to turn them back again?
Hmm?
You see anything?
Yes. I can see their footprints.
No question, this is it.
They make a sharp turn right over there...
Three of them, headed that way.
One's carrying some kind of oversized box.
I wonder how we should kill them.
I can feel the power.
I can feel the blood he gave me coursing through my veins.
And of course we're going to
be ruthless when we kill them.
A way to make a demon turn human again?
There is.
Please tell me how...
You keep your distance from lady Tamayo!
Yushiro.
I'm sorry.
I only threw him. I didn't hit him.
Neither is acceptable.
Right!
Ah, man, that really smarts.
Can you please tell me how?
There's always some kind of medicine or aid,
no matter the wound or ailment.
I don't know how to turn a demon back into a human yet,
but there must be a way.
And I promise we are going to find it.
We are dedicated to establishing such a treatment.
Toward that end, I'd like to
ask you to do something for me.
In order to discover a cure, the first step is
studying the blood of several different demons,
which means I have two favors to ask you.
First, I'd like permission to study your sister's blood.
Second, I need more samples.
I'd like you to retrieve them from demons
as closely related to Kibutsuji as possible.
Nezuko's condition is extremely rare,
perhaps entirely unique.
I understand she was asleep for two straight years.
I believe her body changed during that time.
In most cases,
that long without food, neither human flesh
nor even the blood of some kind of animal,
any demon would undoubtedly grow violent.
Lady Tamayo is as beautiful as ever.
She'll be even more beautiful tomorrow.
However, against all odds,
Nezuko is showing none of those signs.
That miracle could be the key to finding a solution.
Nezuko.
But my second request is not a simple one.
When I say, "demons closely related to Kibutsuji,"
I mean demons with powers such
like those of Kibutsuji himself.
Extracting blood from that kind of demon won't be easy.
What do you think?
Are these requests acceptable, if not pleasant?
If it's really the only way, then I'll do it.
Besides, if you research all that
blood and you can create this medicine,
then it won't just be Nezuko, will it?
A whole lot of other people will be saved, too.
Ah.
Yes, they will.
Get down!
Did you decide how we'll kill them?
Ruthlessly!
Hah! Hah!