Pardon me, sir.
Would it be all right if I took that basket
and some straw and bamboo?
You're more than welcome, for all the good it'll do you.
The basket's full of holes.
Thank you. I'll gladly pay you for it.
No, you don't have to do that.
I don't need it anyway.
Please, I insist.
No, it's fine. Same goes for the straw and bamboo.
Let me pay you!
I said it's fine! So just take it, you stubborn kid!
Take this small offering for your trouble, please!
And thanks a lot for your help!
Nezuko?
Hey, Nezuko?
She's gone!
Hey, Nezuko...
Why'd she dig a hole?
Is my demon kid sister turning into a mole now?
And she doesn't look very happy about it, either.
Guess she really wants to avoid the sun.
Hang on just a second.
Nezuko? Nezuko?
You think you could fit in here?
I want to try to keep moving during the day, too,
but I can carry you, okay?
Can you fit? In here?
Bas-ket.
Uh, guess not.
I can't believe how grown-up she is.
Seems like yesterday she was half that size.
Hey, uh, Nezuko,
remember how you got really big the other day?
I've got an idea. Do you think you could get smaller?
Come on, Nezuko.
Get smaller for me.
Nice job!
Who's a good girl?
You are, Nezuko.
I'm impressed.
Mount Sagiri?
If you really want to go there,
the fastest way is over that mountain.
But the sun's about to set,
and you're hauling an awful lot of luggage.
It's dangerous.
Please don't worry. I'll be careful.
And thank you for the directions.
A lot of people have been going missing
on that mountain lately!
Don't get lost, okay?
It's a temple.
Looks like the light's been left on,
so somebody must be there.
Let's check it out.
That's the scent of blood.
This path can be pretty rough.
Somebody must be hurt!
Is everyone okay?
The hell are you doing here?
This is my territory.
Anybody who sets foot on my turf is gonna have to pay.
It's a demon!
Something's not quite right about you.
Hang on. Are you two human?
A hatchet? Not bad, kid.
Just a little scratch, though.
Should heal in no time.
See that? The bleeding's already stopped.
He's so fast and insanely strong.
You got lucky, but it won't work again.
And now I'm gonna snap your neck!
She...
Nezuko, you killed him!
Wait a minute! But he's a demon!
N-Nezuko.
I don't believe it.
Did that body just move and without a head?
You bastards!
So the girl's a demon after all, huh?
I couldn't tell with that weird vibe you gave off.
But what are you doing teaming up with a human?!
How's he still talking?!
Leave her alone!
Nezuko!
No, Nezuko!
What the hell is with this guy?
Who grows arms out of the side of their head?!
I've gotta help Nezuko!
Out of the way!
So hard.
This kid's head is...
Damn hard!
Yes!
Wrapping my hair around his hatchet
wasn't a great idea. Damn.
Nezuko! Where are you?!
Nezuko!
Get away from her!
I wonder, how many demons are there?
This isn't the scent I found at my house.
It's different, but
I still have to finish him off,
or he'll keep killing people.
So that means I have to do it.
Just do it.
That knife isn't going to do the job.
What's with the mask?
And I couldn't hear his footsteps.
O-Okay.
How do I kill him, then?
Think for yourself.
Or aren't you capable of solving your own problems?
Stabbing the head won't work,
so I'll have to crush it.
I probably have to crush his skull completely,
which means hitting him with this rock over and over.
I bet he'll suffer.
Isn't there any way for me
to finish him off with one blow?
This kid's not going to cut it.
He's far too kind and far too indecisive.
He stands against a demon,
yet the scent of kindness remains.
He still has empathy, even for a demon.
Giyu, this boy will never make it.
I blacked out for a second there.
Does that mean that my body's dead?
I think I'm gonna be sick.
You bastard, I'll kill you!
Get over here!
I'll devour you, damn it!
Now get over here where I can reach you, you little brat!
Hey, aren't you...
I took too long.
The sun's already coming up.
I am gonna enjoy eating you more than...
It only takes that much sunlight to melt him?
No wonder Nezuko was hiding.
Nezuko?
Nezuko!
You're all right.
Hang on. Where's the old guy?
He's holding a burial for the people who got killed.
Excuse me.
My name is Sakonji Urokodaki.
You're the one Giyu Tomioka sent my way, correct?
I am! I'm Tanjiro Kamado,
and my sister's name is Nezuko.
Tanjiro...
What do you intend to do if your sister eats a human?
You're too indecisive.
You must learn to make decisions quickly.
That's why you failed to kill that demon before daybreak.
Do you know why it took you so long
to answer my simple question?
Because your resolve is too weak.
There are two things you must do
if your sister eats a human.
First, you kill her.
Then slit your own belly and die.
That's what traveling alongside a demon
like your sister means.
But you must never allow this to happen,
no matter the cost.
Your sister taking the life of an innocent person
is the one thing that can't happen, ever!
Have I made myself perfectly clear?
Yes!
Very well.
I will test whether or not you are fit
to become a member of the demon slayer corps.
Carry your sister, and follow me!
So fast. But I thought he was an old man!
And, still, I can't hear his footsteps at all!
Nezuko, the ride may be bumpy, but just hang on.
But then, you always did know how to be patient.
Didn't you, Nezuko?
Fixing your kimono again?
That settles it. We'll have to buy you a new one.
No, no, it's fine, really!
This kimono is my favorite.
Besides, it's not important.
I'd rather feed our brothers and sisters.
I swear, I'll turn you back into a human,
and then I'm gonna buy you a beautiful kimono!
Everything I wasn't able to do for the others,
I'll do it all for you!
Okay. Does this... Does this mean...
Please tell me this means that I passed the test.
We're just beginning the test.
We'll be climbing a mountain.
I promise I'll take care of your sister for you
while you're gone.
I do appreciate that, sir.
Oh, man.
I'm so exhausted, my legs are starting to buckle,
and I'm getting dizzy, too.
Now find your way back to my house
at the foot of the mountain.
This time, I won't wait until daybreak.
That's the test?
I get it.
Because of the fog, he thinks I might get lost.
All I have to do is get back by daybreak?
No problem, not with my sense of smell.
I've memorized Mr. Urokodaki's scent.
What the?!
A tiger pit?
Of course.
There are traps all over the mountain.
That's why this is a test.
Oh, no!
Crap, crap, crap.
If I keep walking into these traps,
I'll never make it down the mountain by morning.
Not to mention, besides the traps,
the air here is...
The air is thin on this mountain,
a whole lot thinner than on the mountain where I grew up.
It's no wonder I feel so dizzy.
I can't breathe.
I hope I can make it.
I might pass out.
No, I have to make it!
Control your breathing.
Then sniff out all of those traps.
Yes, got it! Piece of cake!
These traps were set by a human,
which means their scent sticks out to me!
But I guess...
That doesn't solve all my problems,
because I'm still not athletic enough
to dodge every single one of them!
I'll make it back, no matter what...
For Nezuko!
I made it...
Back down.
Dear Urokodaki, sir, forgive the intrusion.
There's a boy headed your way in need of instruction.
He wants to be a demon slayer.
He was fearless enough to try to attack me unarmed.
A demon killed his family,
except for his younger sister, who's been turned,
but I'm certain she will not attack a human.
They're different.
I can sense something about these two.
The boy has a keen sense of smell, much like yourself.
So maybe, just maybe,
he'll be able to find a way to break through.
I'm asking for you to train this boy.
This may seem like a frivolous request, but
please, humor me.
If I'm not mistaken,
this will all make sense one day.
Take care of yourself.
Yours truly, Giyu Tomioka.
You're now my new student, Tanjiro Kamado.