Are you finished changing?
Yes.
Tanjiro...
Now that you have officially
become a demon slayer swordsman,
I would like to explain a few things.
Right.
First,
the demon slayer corps uniform you're wearing
is made with a special kind of fiber.
It's lightweight, water resistant, and nonflammable.
A low-level demon's fangs and talons
are incapable of penetrating that fabric.
It's that strong?
Impressive, hmm?
Now, as for the nichirin sword,
its color varies from owner to owner,
and each hue has its own unique traits.
However, there aren't many
demon slayers with black blades,
so little is known about them.
Some believe they're a bad omen.
What does that mean, "bad omen"? How so?
Black blades are rumored to only be wielded by a
swordsman who has little chance of going very far.
Oh, well.
I don't care if I'm destined for greatness,
because, no matter what, I'll turn Nezuko back.
Yes, you will.
I have no doubt you'll make that happen.
Thank you.
One last thing. Here.
A box to carry your sister during the day,
built from a very light wood called kirikumo cedar.
It's been coated in rock lacquer to reinforce the exterior
and make it even more durable.
Thanks, Urokodaki.
Oh, wow!
You weren't kidding! It is light!
Nezuko, hop in for a ride.
Pretty please?
Nezuko, from now on, we'll always be together.
Okay. I'm off.
Before you go...
Nezuko, how you doing?
Nezuko?
This is only a guess, but I believe
Nezuko can recover her strength by sleeping,
instead of consuming human flesh as other demons do.
Okay. Rest up, Nezuko.
A town to the northwest.
Looks like I found it.
Oh, look. There's Kazumi.
Poor thing. He doesn't look good.
Eh?
Well, he was right next to Satoko when she was taken.
It's happening every night.
It's very creepy.
Tragic. Dreadful!
As soon as night falls, another girl will be abducted.
Mr. Kazumi!
I want to hear what happened last night from you.
This is where Satoko vanished,
but I'm sure you don't believe me.
I do believe you.
I'm here to help.
Now let's see!
There's still a faint scent of the demon here...
But it's uneven.
Something's off.
Who is this kid, anyway?
How dare you?!
You lost her?!
You bastard!
That's enough! Honey, please, stop!
I want you to believe me.
She really did just vanish.
I know.
That's why I came here, so I can stop this.
Are you really gonna keep going?
Yes.
Come on. It's getting late.
I'm flattered that you're so concerned
about this, but shouldn't you rest,
maybe pick it up again in the morning?
They're only active at night...
So there's no time for rest.
Got something.
There's a new scent in the area.
It's nearby. It won't be long now.
Wait a second.
Don't tell me you're a...
are you a...
It's terrifying.
I want you to stay indoors, where you'll be safe.
I will, mother.
Good night. I'm going to bed.
I wonder what happened to the girls who disappeared.
I hope they're all right.
Hey, wait! Where are you going?!
So fast.
The scent got stronger!
The demon's active!
How'd he do that?
He said, "demon."
Demon? Then he's...
This is it. They're right here.
Two scents... one demon, one human girl.
I don't see them.
Although...
The scent is strongest right...
Here!
The demon has powers!
The blood demon art
is a special spell that some use to give them abilities.
You may end up having to face some
of them in the near future as well.
What did you do with the girls you kidnapped?!
There are some things I wanna know!
Who was that?
I need your help.
Hold her for me, and stay close.
As long as you do that, I can protect you!
The ground, the wall,
I bet it could come from just about anywhere.
I wouldn't be surprised if it
could appear out of thin air.
Doesn't matter, because, even if it's submerged,
it can't erase its scent.
Now.
Water breathing! Fifth form!
There are more!
Take it easy.
You've got this!
Eighth form!
Waterfall basin!
Tanjiro, listen to me closely.
There's only one demon that has the kind
of blood that can turn a human, just one,
that's it, in the entire world.
Just one?
The first demon there ever was.
He's been here for more than a thousand years.
He's your target, the one who attacked your family.
More importantly, I believe he's also the one
who might know how to turn your sister back into a human.
That demon's name is...
Muzan Kibutsuji.
Eighth form! Waterfall basin!
I missed.
I missed all the vulnerable spots,
because I switched forms midway through.
They all have the same exact scent.
Usually, demons don't work together.
Which means one demon has split into three.
I have to take them all out
and still protect these two.
Don't lose your nerve.
Make him talk to you
about Muzan Kibutsuji
and about how to turn a demon back into a human!
Total concentration.
Water breathing!
Second form! Water wheel!
Missed again.
I can't chase him,
and I can't take a full swing while
I'm protecting these two, either.
Bastard!
She'll go stale!
Move out of the way, you little punk!
The girl's 16 already. She's losing flavor by the second!
If I don't eat her soon, there won't be any left at all!
Take a breath, other me.
Calm down. No big deal.
Nights like this happen, right?
I've already feasted on plenty
of this town's 16-year-old girls,
and every one of them was meaty and delicious.
I am satisfied with that.
Well, I'm not satisfied at all, other me!
I want to devour all of them!
You monster!
Bring Satoko back,
the girl you took the other night!
Satoko?
Which one was that?
If her hairpin is in this collection,
then I'm afraid I've already eaten her.
Sorry.
I missed again.
He moves so fast!
Oh, crap! I'm too close to the wall!
Why in the world would a demon
be traveling with a mere human?
What's the meaning of this?
Who are these two?
Why would a swordsman and demon be working together?
It doesn't make any sense.
Nezuko.
I don't know if this will be of any comfort or not,
but while Nezuko was asleep,
I used hypnotic suggestion on her.
What for?
I convinced her that all humans are her family.
I told her to protect them.
"The demons are your enemies."
Nezuko!
"If a demon harms a human,
never forgive them!"