How?
How in the world could something like this happen?
Come on, Nezuko!
I've got you! Don't die on me!
No matter what it takes, I'll save you!
I won't let you die.
I promise I'll save you.
Your big brother's got you!
Tanjiro.
Your face is all covered in soot.
Let me clean you up.
You know, you really don't have to go.
All this snow could be dangerous.
I want us to have a good new year's celebration
where everyone can eat as much as they want,
so I'll sell all the charcoal I can.
How thoughtful.
Hey, bro!
Are you going to town again today?
I'm coming with you!
No, you're not.
You know you can't walk as fast as Tanjiro can, sweetie.
Aw, come on, mom!
No way.
He's not going to be able to use the cart today,
which means he can't give you a ride when you get tired.
Tanjiro!
I wanna come with you.
I promise I'll help out.
That's very generous of you, Hanako.
But no.
You're staying home today.
Sorry, Shigeru. You are, too.
But I'll bring back goodies, okay?
Promise?
Yeah.
And, Hanako,
I'll read for you when I get home later.
'Kay!
Good girl.
Thank you for doing this, Tanjiro.
'Course.
Time for me to head out.
Hey, Takeo, do me a favor while I'm gone, okay?
Chop as much wood as you can.
Yeah, I was already gonna do that anyway.
But I was kinda hoping we'd do
that together this time. Hmph.
There, there, now.
Knock it off, would you?!
You're blushing, take!
Shut up, you brat!
There, there, now.
I told you to cut it out!
Come back as soon as you can, okay?
Be safe, and see you when you get back!
Hi, Tanjiro.
Hey, Nezuko.
I had to put Rokuta down for a nap now.
Otherwise, he would throw a fit.
Ever since dad passed, he's been glued to your side.
In fact, everyone seems to follow you wherever you go.
I'll see you when you get back!
We don't exactly have an easy life, but we're happy.
Life can change, though,
as sudden as the weather.
It shifts and moves on.
The sun can't shine forever,
and the snow has to stop at some point.
But whatever happens, when happiness is destroyed,
it's always followed by the smell of blood.
Ah, Tanjiro!
You came down the mountain on a day like today?
Don't you ever stop working? You could catch a cold.
It's not as bad as you think.
You need a refill on charcoal, by any chance?
Hey, Tanjiro!
Eh?
I'll take some more!
I'm good, but thanks for fixing
my sliding doors the other day.
I need some charcoal, too!
Tanjiro!
I'm so glad you're here!
I've been accused of breaking this plate!
Can you help me out here?
Give it a sniff!
It smells like a cat to me.
You see?
So it really was a cat.
I tried to tell you I didn't do it!
Hey there, Tanjiro!
I don't suppose you could give me
a hand with this luggage, could you?
How'd it get so late?
Oh, well. At least I sold out.
Hang on! Tanjiro!
Eh?
You're not going back up the mountain now.
It's simply too dangerous.
Oh, I'll be fine. I've got a good nose.
You can stay here for the night.
Come on. Get inside.
No, I'm..
Don't argue. Just get in here...
Before the demons show up.
Thanks for dinner.
Hey, uh, Mr. Saburo, what did you mean by "demons"?
There have always been man-eating
demons prowling about after dark.
That's why it's not safe to go outside at night.
Time for bed.
You can set off for home at first light.
These demons,
they're not able to come inside your house, are they?
Yes, they could come in.
But, then, wouldn't they just eat everyone?
The demon slayers protect us
by killing as many as they can.
They always have.
Now go to sleep.
It's lights out.
Old man Saburo,
he's been on his own since he lost his family.
He must be lonely.
I'll bring my brothers and sisters by.
You don't have to be scared.
There are no demons. You're safe.
Although, now that I think of it,
my grandma used to say the same thing
before she passed away.
You be careful now.
Thank you!
Whenever happiness is destroyed...
It's always followed...
Eh?
The smell of blood.
Nezuko!
What happened?! What's going on here?!
What happened to you?!
Mom?
Mom. Hanako.
Takeo. Shigeru.
Nezuko. Rokuta.
Nezuko's the only one who's still warm.
If I can get her to a doctor, she might live.
How could something like this happen?
Maybe a bear...
That couldn't find a place to hibernate?
I can't breathe!
The air is icy! My lungs hurt!
Just keep moving!
Move those legs of yours faster!
We've still got a long way to go to get to town. Hurry!
I won't let you die.
No matter what it takes,
your big brother will save you!
Oh, no!
The snow saved me...
But the snow is the only reason I fell.
Nezuko?
Nezuko, are you okay?
You don't have to walk!
Let me carry you to town, all right?
Nezuko!
Sh-she's...
A demon!
This is what old man Saburo tried to tell me about.
She's a man-eating demon?
Impossible! Nezuko's a human
since the day she was born!
Except she doesn't have Nezuko's scent anymore.
But she isn't the one who killed them.
She was lying on top of Rokuta
like she was protecting him,
and her hands and mouth weren't covered in blood,
but there was one more. There was another scent!
How are you getting bigger?!
And she's getting stronger, too!
While I was sleeping like a baby at Saburo's,
you were all being brutally murdered!
It must have hurt.
You suffered, didn't you?
I'm sorry I wasn't there to help.
I have to at least save Nezuko, though!
But she's too strong for me to do anything!
Nezuko! Hang on, Nezuko!
Don't give in! You gotta hang on!
Don't let it take control!
You gotta stay strong!
Just hang on! Please!
Eh?
What the...
Who's that?
A sword?
Why are you protecting it?
She's my sister!
I was taking her to get help!
Nezuko!
You call that thing your sister?
Don't move!
My job is to slay every demon I find,
which means I have to decapitate your sister here.
No, wait!
Nezuko hasn't hurt anyone!
Back at my house,
there was another scent I'd never smelled before!
That's probably the one who killed my family!
Nezuko didn't do it!
I don't know why she's changed into something like this,
but still...
It's really quite simple.
She's turned because her wounds
were exposed to demon blood.
That's how the man-eating monsters multiply.
Nezuko would never eat a human!
You must be joking.
If I hadn't gotten here when I
did, she would have devoured you.
You're wrong! She wouldn't hurt me!
She knows I'm her big brother!
And I won't let her hurt anyone!
I'll turn her back into a human!
I will heal her!
She can't be healed.
Once you become a demon, no one can ever turn back.
There's a way,
and I'll find it, no matter what it takes,
so please let her live!
I'll hunt down the one who slaughtered my family!
I promise I'll make everything right! Please!
Just let her go!
Please don't do this!
Don't, don't take anyone else away from me.
I'm begging you.
Please...
Don't kill my little sister.
Please don't do it!
I'm begging you.
Don't grovel like that and give
your enemies the chance to kill you!
All you're doing is making yourself vulnerable!
If it were even a little bit effective,
your family would still be alive right now!
How can a weakling like you have any
hope of finding a way to heal his sister
or hunt down a demon?!
Don't be ridiculous!
The weak have no rights.
They don't get to make choices! All they can
do is be relentlessly crushed by the strong!
Now, maybe the demons know of a way to cure your sister.
Maybe! But don't think for even a moment that
any one of them is going to respect your wishes,
just like I have no respect for you!
That's reality.
And why the hell did you throw
yourself over her like that?
Was that your way of protecting her?
Why didn't you swing that hatchet?
And why would you ever turn your back to me?
Those mistakes are what led to her capture!
I could have easily just skewered
the both of you and been done with it!
Don't cry.
Don't succumb to sorrow.
This isn't the time to despair.
I know you're devastated right now.
Your family massacred. Your sister a demon.
I know it hurts.
I know you want to scream.
I understand.
If only I'd gotten here half a day sooner,
maybe then, your family would still be alive.
However, there's no way to turn back time,
so feel it.
Feel the pure rage of being unable to forgive.
Let it be what gives you the strength to take action.
With that fragile resolve of yours,
you can't protect your sister or heal her,
and you'll never get revenge
for what happened to your family!
No!
Don't you touch her!
You let your emotion drive you to charge at me.
You are a fool!
Huh? What happened to the hatchet?
Right before he went behind that tree...
He threw the rock, and, at the same time,
he tossed the hatchet.
He was only pretending to attack me
so I wouldn't realize he was unarmed.
He knew he had no way of beating me.
His whole plan was to bring me
down after I'd knocked him out.
This kid.
Damn it!
She'll kill him!
Nezuko...
Nezuko didn't do it.
She'd never eat a human!
Long ago,
someone else said the same thing,
only to end up being devoured.
A starving demon will eat anyone,
its own brothers, sisters, parents.
They're rich in nutrients.
I've seen it more times than I can count.
This girl has been badly wounded.
She's using up a lot of energy to heal herself.
And surely most of her strength
was drained during her transformation,
so there's no question.
She's starving right now.
She must have been craving a feast right from the start,
even her own brother,
but she protected him
and turned her attention to me.
I wonder if...
Just maybe...
These two are different.
We have to leave you behind, Tanjiro.
I'm so sorry.
Take care of Nezuko.
You awake?
Get to mount Sagiri as soon as possible.
Look for an old man named Sakonji Urokodaki.
When you find him, tell him Giyu Tomioka sent you.
It's cloudy, so she seems to be all right at the moment,
but never let her be exposed to sunlight.
Let's go.