Gotcha!
Nice one.
Rui? Rui!
Rui! What are you doing?
You know you're not supposed to be outside!
Since the day I was born, I've always been very frail.
I couldn't run. Even just walking was a struggle for me.
That is... Until Master Muzan appeared.
You poor thing. I'll save you from this harsh life.
My parents weren't happy about it.
Since I'd acquired a strong body, I could never expose
myself to sunlight, and of course I had to devour humans.
What have you done? What on earth have you done, Rui?
Answer me!
Long ago, I heard a wonderful story.
There was once a Father who died
trying to save his drowning child.
I was deeply moved.
Such astounding display of parental love, a true bond.
This Father who drowned
had fulfilled his role as a guardian wonderfully,
but I wasn't bestowed the same kind of devotion.
When it came to my own parents, they tried to kill me.
All my Mother did was cry,
never lifting a finger to protect me.
They must have been imposters.
Our bond wasn't the genuine one at all, I thought.
I'm... Sorry.
She's saying something. I thought she was dead.
I'm sorry...
That I couldn't give you a strong, healthy body.
Those... Were the last words my Mother ever spoke to me.
She was dead.
Rui, listen. We're going to die with you!
I was so enraged he had tried to kill me,
the meaning of his words escaped me.
But I came to realize soon after
he intended to atone on my behalf
for the sin of having killed someone,
in the form of taking his own life.
It was a genuine bond,
and that night, I had severed it with my own two hands.
After all that, however,
Master Muzan gave me words of encouragement.
It was all your parents's fault for refusing to
accept you for who you are. Take pride in your own power.
I had no other choice but to see it that way.
I couldn't bear the weight of what I'd done.
I knew that I only had myself to blame.
Every single day,
I missed my parents so much, I could barely stand it.
Even after crafting a family of my own,
that emptiness remained.
Because I was the strongest,
I couldn't depend on anyone to protect me, no one.
The more powerful I became, the more distant
my memories of being human became as well.
I began losing sight
of what it was I wanted in the first place.
I sought out a bond that I was
never able to claim for myself,
not in my old life, nor the new one I created.
This body is giving off a scent,
one of grief too overwhelming for him to bear.
So warm. Hands as gentle as sunbeams.
I remember now, clear as day. I had wanted to apologize.
I'm sorry. I was... I was to blame for everything.
I hope you can forgive me.
I've killed so many people, though.
Surely I'm going to hell, aren't I?
Father, Mother,
I can't go to the same place as you, can I?
That's not true.
We'll be together, no matter where you go.
Rui.
Oh, Father... And Mother.
Darling. We'll be with you always.
It was my fault. All of it was my
fault. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry! Forgive me!
Don't waste your sympathy. It was a demon.
The fact it looked like a child makes no difference.
It lived for decades, terrorizing our people.
If it's for the sake of avenging those who were killed,
to make sure there are no more victims,
I won't hesitate
to bring my blade down on any demon's neck.
But when it comes to those who felt despair and regret
from the actions they took as a demon,
I will never disrespect them!
Because at one time or another...
They were human, no different from me!
So please don't step on his remains!
They're not hideous monsters at all.
Instead, demons are hopeless creatures, tragic creatures.
Isn't she...
Oh, my.
Why would you get in my way, Tomioka?
And after you told me we could never
be friends with demons. I have to say...
This kind of thing is exactly why no one likes you.
Incredible. This antidote of Lady Kocho's
is very effective, isn't it?
Indeed, and she prepared it after a mere glance
at this situation. She's truly amazing. As is he.
That boy? How so?
He defeated that demon, which in turn,
slowed the circulation of the poison just a bit.
All right! This should do it! We're in good shape.
Looks like they'll all pull through.
That's good. I'd like to wrap things up as quickly
as possible and leave this place. Wouldn't you?
No argument here.
This mountain has a really hideous stench to it.
Now then, Tomioka, would you please move?
I don't... I don't think I'm disliked.
Oh, dear. I do apologize.
You're only just hearing about this now, then?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean for you to find out this way.
Boy!
Yes, ma'am!
What you're protecting there is actually a demon,
so please move away before you get hurt.
No. You're mistaken! Well, you're not
mistaken, but she's my little sister!
She's my sister, and that's why...
Oh, my. Is that really true? You poor thing.
In that case, so she won't suffer,
I'll use a gentle toxin in order to kill her.
Can you move?
Even if it's difficult, you need to go.
Take your sister, and run.
Tomioka...
Thank you. I appreciate this!
Did you... Just break the rules of the Corps?
My whole body is aching so much, I wanna scream,
but I have to keep going and endure it!
Endure! Endure! Endure! Endure!
Does this mean
I'm gonna have to leave the Demon Slayer Corps?
Even if she's my sister, there's no way
they'd let one of their swordsmen travel with a demon!
I see you're dead serious about this.
Who would have thought a Hashira would defend a demon?
Whatever your intentions are, I'm afraid I don't
feel like playing this game of stalling for time,
and so good day to you.
Is this your attempt at catching up with me?
I don't have any objections to you trying to stop me,
but don't forget there's someone else to watch out for.
Don't stop running! Keep on moving!
You gotta run as far away as you can!
Damn it! What just happened? I
wasn't aware of my surroundings. Nezuko!
A Demon Slayer?
Get out of here, Nezuko! Run away as fast as you can!
Don't get caught, no matter what! Hurry!
Did she just shrink into a child?
She's just running away
without even throwing out an attack. Why?
Well, it doesn't matter. My orders are to slay this demon.
Tomioka... There's something I want to say.
Since the purpose of my attack was to slay a demon,
it certainly wouldn't be construed
as a violation of the Corps,
but what you're doing is clearly against the rules.
You're preventing me from slaying a demon.
What are your intentions here?
Don't you have anything to say for yourself? This will be
your final warning. At least give me some sort of reason.
As I recall, it was two years ago.
Are you about to go into a long-winded story
from the past just to spite me?
It's because of what I said to you earlier. Is that it?
Message! Message!
I have a message from headquarters!
Tanjiro and Nezuko are to be taken into custody
and brought back to headquarters!
Tanjiro and the demon Nezuko are to be taken
into custody and brought back to headquarters!
Tanjiro, dressed in a checkered Haori,
with a scar on his forehead!
Nezuko, a demon girl with a bamboo muzzle!
Are you Nezuko?
Bring them back! Bring them back!
Tanjiro, dressed in a checkered Haori,
with a scar on his forehead!
Nezuko, a demon girl with a bamboo muzzle!
Bring them back! Bring them back!
He does have a scar.
All right, let's bring him in.
Look. His jawbone seems to be broken, doesn't it?
I feel bad about tying him up.
Wh-who the hell is this?
I don't know. A demon? No, it couldn't be.
Is it human?
He's wearing our uniform trousers.
Oh, wait. This is a mask. He is human!
All right, let's bring him in.
Ah, this guy's been beaten up really bad.
Why's he strung up like this?
There was nothing I could do.
On my own, I couldn't bring down even a single demon.
You know what? Maybe I'm not that strong.
They wrapped us all up, huh?
Who are these people?
They seem to be cleaning up this place really efficiently.
And that girl there,
isn't she the girl from final selection?
She has the same kind of hair ornament
as the lady who wrapped us up.
Should we bring them as well?
Yes, go to the butterfly mansion. I'll be
hunting down the demons here, so you can rest easy.
I think I've heard of these guys.
They're called the Kakushi.
They clean up the aftermath
of the Corps's battles with demons.
I've heard that most of their members
are people whose sword skills aren't quite as polished.
It's daybreak.
Wake up. I said wake up! You gotta...
Hey, can you even hear me? Come on! Get up!
Are you gonna sleep all day?
Wake the hell up, will you?!
You're in the presence of the Hashira!