Beast breathing.
Seventh form, spatial awareness.
You find them?
Yeah. Follow me that way!
I'm sensing a strong presence over there.
You are? Way to go, Inosuke!
Why, you...
We can't get anywhere with these guys around!
Damn it. Isn't there...
isn't there any way we can get out of this?
Nez...N-N-Nezuko.
Nez... where are you?
N-N-N-Nezuko!
The hell with this crap!
That's it!
I'm just gonna demolish them all at once!
Stop it. You can't!
There must be a way to save them.
Listen. We can't hurt these people.
M-Murata?
Leave these guys to me, and go on ahead, Tanjiro!
Big talk from the guy who pissed his pants!
I never did anything of the sort, you stupid boar!
I wasn't even talking to you, so butt out!
I know I wasn't very brave back there,
but I'm still a Demon Slayer!
I'll find a way to hold them off.
I know now I just need to cut the threads
and that their movement patterns are very basic,
so I should be fine.
I'll watch out for the spiders, too.
There have to be people who are under even
greater control that are closer to the demon.
You have to help them!
I got it! Stay strong.
Let's go, Inosuke!
Hey, let go of me, damn it!
I wanna pound that guy's face in first!
Who's he calling "a stupid boar"?
Oh, shut up!
Stop messing around, and get out of here!
I'm gonna make you see stars when I get back!
Mark my words!
damn it! I can't wait to get back and pummel that guy.
Stop talking like that!
Didn't you hear him call me a "stupid boar," monjiro?
My name's Tanjiro!
Anyway, are we headed the right way?
My senses have never led me astray.
Although, I...
What are all these annoying threads?
It must mean we're closing in on the demon.
There's another group here.
Stop.
Don't come any closer.
You have to go and bring someone here who's a higher rank!
It's the only way for certain to
stop the rest of us from being killed!
Help us.
I beg you!
I wonder if you can defeat them.
The closer that someone is able to get to me,
the stronger these threads of mine become,
as do my precious dolls.
Mother...
Can you really win?
Rui.
Don't you think this is taking too much time?
You'd better get to it,
or I'm gonna have to tell father.
No, I can do it!
You don't have to worry! I promise to protect you!
So, please, whatever you do,
don't tell your father, not him!
Well, then, hurry it up.
Die, all of you! Just die already!
It'll be hell for me if I don't get rid of you!
Run away!
So fast!
I'm being controlled, so my movements aren't...
My own!
I was never anywhere near as strong as this!
The demon that's controlling her has no
concern for the strain it's putting on her body.
This is cruel.
Stubborn imbeciles.
Take this!
That sound.
Please, end my life.
All the bones...
In my arms and legs...
They're broken, piercing my insides.
Every time I'm forced to move,
the pain is unbearable.
I can't take it anymore.
Either way, I'll die.
So, please...
Just hurry up, and finish the job.
I'll take on the job.
Wait!
Inosuke!
We gotta find a way to save him!
Oh, shut up!
You need to stop your bellyachin'!
Listen to me!
He's asking us to put him out of his misery, all right?
These guys are speedy, too.
If we get caught nappin', we'll be done for!
I know that! Just give me a moment to think.
I don't want to attack them,
but cutting the strings won't have a lasting effect.
How can we stop them from moving?
I've got it!
Eh? Hey!
Good. She's following me.
The hell?
Why are you running around in circles like that?
Quit messin' around!
total concentration.
Huh?
So strong.
Great! Looks like it worked out!
Wha...
What the heck was that just now?!
I wanna do it, too!
Come at me!
You see that?!
Whatever you can do, I can do just as well!
Sorry. I must have missed it.
You're kidding!
I'm a little busy at the moment!
Damn! They are all such useless puppets.
I have no choice but to unleash that one, then.
Nezuko!
Where are you?!
Nezuko,
Tanjiro,
Chuntaro, even the wild boar,
where did you all go?!
I'm sorry for everything, okay?
Chuntaro?
You decided to come check in on me?
You're so wonderful and adorable, Chuntaro!
Not as adorable as Nezuko, but I'd say a close second!
I really appreciate this!
I'm sorry for everything!
How about we just start fresh
and go look for Nezuko together?
Check that out!
I've tossed up more of 'em than you have now!
That's good. Just one more.
Okay. I'm gonna do it one more time, so watch!
All right, fine. I'll watch.
Just try not to hurt him!
These puppets are weak!
I don't need them anymore!
They're useless!
Damn it to hell.
That thing went and killed all of 'em!
Let's go.
No arguments here.
it's this way!
We'll reach them before you know it.
Now that the wind's changed direction,
my sense of smell is returning.
Then I'll know exactly where it is.
There! I'm picking up two more scents!
Inosuke!
I detected that thing before you did.
I'm gonna hack its head right off its shoulders!
Huh?
That thing...
Doesn't even have a head!
Nezuko!
Where are you?!
Where the heck are you, Tanjiro?
You, too, Inosuke. Don't just leave me
here all by myself in this terrifying forest!
What was that?
You know what?
This is starting to make me really mad.
I'm gonna find Nezuko and then
say goodbye to this creepy forest.
Nezuko!
This thing's got no weak spots.
Where am I supposed to cut it?
Inosuke.
What do we do? What do we do?!
Calm down. Listen closely, all right?
Slash from the right part of the
neck to the left part of its waist.
It'll be tough.
It's a lot of mass to cover. That said...
No, wait! Don't go alone!
It's fast.
I can still dodge it, though!
That's right!
Those spiders!
I can't move.
I'm a dead man!
Inosuke, this is a tough one,
but we can do it.
If we put our heads together,
we'll be able to win!
Damn you!
Don't go making me feel giddier than I already do!
This thing's in my way!
Here! Launch yourself!
Now jump! Go for it!
Total concentration. Water breathing.
Fourth form...
Striking tide!
You're up, Inosuke!
It seems like he's got everything figured out.
I gotta say that's pretty irritating.
It's almost like he can predict the future.
It's as natural for him as water flowing from a river.
It's not about going first for this kid.
It's all about the battle itself
and watching it flow like a raging current!
Great! He cut it perfectly.
All right, Inosuke! You defeated it!
Hmm? What's wrong?
I'll prove to that idiot
anything he can do, I can do, too!
A scent?
So that's why you did that, Inosuke!
No.
That doll was my fastest and
strongest, and they still won!
It's Rui's fault for coming to me with his threats!
That's why I panicked.
It's not my fault.
From above?
Water breathing! First form...
He's going to cut my head off!
Oh, what do I do? What do I do?!
a-although...
If I die, I'll be freed.
I'll find peace.
Fifth form,
blessed rain after the drought.
This feeling,
it's like I'm being showered by a gentle rain.
It doesn't hurt, not at all.
I just feel warm.
I never dreamed my end would be this tranquil.
And now I'll be released.
I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to make you so angry!
Tell me, what was it that infuriated you?
It's your own fault for not realizing what made him angry.
But how could I?
Looks like mother's in trouble with father again.
No! Stop! No more!
Those eyes.
Such kind eyes.
When I was human, I think there was someone
who used to look at me with those same kind eyes.
I wonder who that was.
I can't remember.
I just know that it was someone who always cherished me.
I wonder...
How that person is doing now.
Someone from the Twelve Kizuki is here.
W-Wait!
Be careful.
A member of the Twelve Kizuki,
they're here on this mountain,
just within my grasp.