The Twelve Kizuki should possess
a high amount of Kibutsuji's blood.
If I can extract it,
the medicine that'll help Nezuko will be finished sooner.
Inosuke's still back there.
So did you take out that monster?
Hey, are you okay? You're bleeding.
I asked you if you defeated that thing or not!
Uh, yeah, I did!
But enough about that. Your wounds...
Don't go showering me with your
mushy sensitivity and kindness!
I don't need it. You got that?
After all, anything you can do, I can do, too!
Before you know it, my head will be...
my head will be even harder than yours.
Not to mention that...
not to mention... not to mention...
He's not doing well.
And I couldn't save our other friends, either.
That woman gave off a scent of terror and suffering...
enough to make her yearn for death.
What is it about this mountain, anyway?
A Demon family living here...
As well as one of the Twelve Kizuki?
I didn't think demons gathered together like that.
Ouch!
Ow!
Something just pricked me.
What the hell? I'm so frustrated.
I can't find Tanjiro or Inosuke anywhere!
Where did they go?
Great! Now what?
Something really stinks around here, too! Gross!
I think I'm gonna cry.
And the sound of these spiders
running around is so creepy.
I'm sure they're just doing their best
to survive, the same as me, but still!
Be quiet! Stop moving around!
what am I even looking at?!
Why did that spider have a human face on it?!
What is happening right now?! What is happening?!
Please be a dream! Please be a dream!
If I wake up right now, I promise to work harder!
If I were to wake up in the presence of
my precious Nezuko, then I'll do anything!
I'll do hard manual labor.
I'll even plow fields, a whole acre, no, two!
I promise!
Let me wake up from this nightmare!
The heck is that?
Are those humans who got turned into spiders?
Is that house floating?
I can't quite make it out, but are those threads?
And it really stinks!
Talk about pungent!
Tanjiro would hate this for sure!
The smell is making my throat hurt!
Not just that. It's irritating my eyes, too,
It's huge!
Look at the size of that thing!
It's absolutely gigantic!
You better not start talking to me!
I don't wanna hear it from you!
There's no point in running away!
You've already lost the battle!
I told you not to talk to me!
I don't wanna hear it, so stop talking!
Things like you give me the creeps, all right?
So you already know how dire the situation is for you.
What are you talking about?
Hah! Take a look at your hands.
My hands? Why?
What's wrong with my ha...
What's this?
You're poisoned.
A spider bit you, didn't it?
You're gonna turn into one before long.
In half an hour, you'll be my
slave, crawling all over the ground!
Do you understand?
Here. I'll use this watch to explain.
By the time this long hand goes around once,
you'll have become one of the spiders.
When the hand arrives here...
You'll feel tingling and pain in your limbs.
When it's here, you'll feel dizzy and nauseous.
Here, your body will painfully
start to shrink, and you'll black out.
And by the time you wake up...
Huh?
Running away...
Is useless! I know!
But you're crazy if you think
I'm not gonna try and get away!
What do you think you're doing?
Shut up! Shut up! Just you shut up!
There's no need to be afraid.
Once the transformation has taken effect,
you'll lose your humanity.
Exactly!
That's just what I've been dreading about all this!
Why can't you get that through your head, huh?!
Someone like you wouldn't have
anyone special in their lives!
Maybe some more poison would help
so we can speed up the process for you.
No, not that!
Stay away from me!
I don't want to turn into one of those things!
Get ahold of yourself!
Stop crying and running away!
Doing that isn't going to get you anywhere!
Come down from there!
You hear me, Zenitsu?
We're going to continue training!
If I go through another one of
your training regimens, I'm gonna die!
I'm not gonna be able to handle it!
You're not going to die,
not from this!
Come down from there, you fool!
Come on, gramps!
Address me as "master"!
But I wanna call you gramps, 'cause I love you!
When the girl I loved made me raise
money so she could run off with another guy,
you rescued me from my mountain of debt!
Maybe all you wanted was to be able to train a swordsman,
but I want to live up to your expectations, too!
I don't know that I can, though.
I feel terrible about the fact that I'm like this.
I really do! Just so you know,
I've been skipping out on sleep so that I can train more,
but I have absolutely nothing to show for it!
Why?! Seriously, is there some reason I don't know about?!
Calm yourself, Zenitsu!
The potential lies within you!
I've had enough of it all!
Zenitsu, are you okay?!
Getting hit by lighting...
How unlucky can you get?
That's when my hair color changed.
I was thankful just to be alive, but even so...
I-I hate myself more than anyone else.
I always try to get my act together, but I
just end up running away or cowering in fear.
I'm pathetic.
I want to change. I want to be a capable individual.
The fact is...
I'm doing absolutely everything that I can!
But I still have to be turned
into some horrific spider creature?!
It can't be! Say it isn't true!
What's up with this guy?
He's a strange one.
Oh, crap! Don't climb up here!
Can't you leave me alone for just a little bit?!
This is all too much for me to handle right now!
Eh? Huh?
My hair's falling out already?
Wait. My hair.
Hey, he never mentioned that part to me!
Huh?
I don't understand this guy at all.
Isn't he a Demon slayer who came here to kill our family?
But he fainted.
How spineless can you get?
He's gonna fall on his head and die.
What the hell?
Thunder breathing technique. First form...
Huh?
Poison sputum!
Did he just twist his body in midair?
With such quick reflexes, I hardly recognize him.
thunder breathing. First form...
Hey, you guys, go take him down!
Thunder breathing, first form...
He's been going into that same stance over and over.
Ah, I know why he's doing that.
He must only be capable of that one attack.
Don't worry about it, Zenitsu.
That's good enough progress.
Mastering even one is cause for celebration.
If you can only do one thing, hone it to perfection.
Work on refining it to its utmost potential.
But, gramps, just a little while ago,
you were really angry,
because thunder breathing has six forms,
and all I can manage to do is one.
Do you know what the process of forging a sword is?
I don't know.
I wish he'd stop hitting me.
I'm gonna cry.
When making a sword, you hammer
and hammer to get rid of impurities
and anything else you don't need.
The greater the purity of the blade,
the more durable it becomes.
Is that why you keep clobbering me day in and day out?
But I'm not made of steel.
I'm living flesh.
You're not much of a threat, are you?
And you call yourself a Demon slayer?
Any minute now, you'll be
rendered immobile by that poison.
Zenitsu, perfect it!
It's all right to cry or go off by yourself.
Just don't ever give up.
Believe in yourself.
You endured all that hellish training.
You'll be rewarded for that without question.
Work to forge yourself like a tempered blade
and become the most resilient of all!
Focus on what you do best!
Get out of here.
Huh?
You gonna make me repeat myself?
Leave my sight.
You know why.
The way you cry like a baby all day long,
aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Good for nothing.
Any effort spent on you is an absolute waste of time.
Our teacher is an extraordinary man.
But gramps told me that...
Hey, you,
don't go being all familiar and calling him "gramps"!
He's a former Hashira, someone who earned
the highest title in the Demon slayer corps!
Hardly anyone ever gets the chance
to be trained by a former Hashira.
The time he spends training you is all for nothing.
It's infuriating to see!
I hate even looking at you, so get out!
Why are you even here?
Why do you insist on clinging on like a patch of mold?!
I have no parents,
no one who has hopes for me,
no one with dreams that eventually, one day,
I'll be able to accomplish something important...
Not even a thing as simple as
proving myself useful to someone,
either by protecting them or making them happy,
just once in my life.
I have no one like that.
If you mess up or cry or run away even once,
everyone says, "oh, this guy's no good," and walk away.
Or so I thought.
Time and time again, gramps would run me through my paces.
I tried running away on numerous occasions.
But each time I did...
He'd drag me right back.
He smacked me around a little too much for my liking,
but he never abandoned me.
Get him! Inject more poison into his veins!
That should do it.
Eh?
What's this?
The air is vibrating.
Thunder breathing. First form,
thunderclap and flash!
Sixfold!
He vanished?
Did I get slashed? Me?
It can't be!
To think, by someone like him.
This is ridiculous!
I was defeated by someone who
could hardly move their limbs!
I just wanna dream
a happy, peaceful dream.
In it, I'm more powerful than anyone.
I'm able to help the weak,
anyone in trouble anytime...
And everything that gramps taught me,
all the time and effort he spent,
it wasn't for nothing.
In this dream, thanks to gramps,
I became strong and was able to help a lot of people.
But the time for dreams is over now.
Is that you, Chuntaro?
I'm so sorry.
Don't ever give up!
"don't ever give up."
I can use the breathing technique to slow down the poison.
Even if it's painful,
even if it's agonizing,
don't try to take the easy way out,
or gramps will let you have it.
Yeah, and Tanjiro's gonna yell at you, too.
What was that sound?
Did lightning just strike?
How should I know?
Well, I'm not smelling any thunderclouds,
but that odor got stronger and
is messing with my senses again.
Inosuke!
What?
I think I'm gonna go take that path instead.
Why are you telling me? Do whatever you want!
So are you headed back down?
Back down?
Down the mountain, I mean.
Why would I do that? Just beat it!
What about all your wounds, though?
What are you talking about?!
I'm not hurt at all!
What?
You've gotta be kidding, Inosuke.
Anyone from a mile away could see how bloodied you are.
Eh?
Huh?
A Demon!
The scent hanging over this mountain
blocked me from picking that up!
Listen up, you damn Demon!
I'm gonna tear you to shreds!
Get back here!
Hang on!
Now, father!
Who are you callin' "father"?
Inosuke!
Don't you come near my family!
Stay away from them!
I'm leaving the rest to you...
Father.
Water breathing. Second form,
water wheel!