Tanjiro.
You didn't.
Did you think I joined the Demon Slayer Corps because
I thought it was gonna be all sunshine and rainbows?!
Well, I...
Guys like you should be erased
from this world immediately!
You shall face justice! Don't ever disrespect the Corps!
Hi, Nezuko!
How are you today?
Where are you going, Nezuko?
Wait for me!
Zenitsu, stop following her already!
Tanjiro...
Let's be best friends, Tanjiro!
Zenitsu, why are you following
us around like this? Stop it!
Oh, come on, don't be a stranger, Tanjiro!
You've got to cut this out right now!
Man, I'm hungry.
Pardon me, good sir.
I cannot help but notice those
clothes of yours are rather soiled.
It would be my pleasure to clean them for
you, so please wear these in the meantime.
I believe you will find them
comfortable and pleasant to the touch.
I was thinking of making some
tempura for dinner, you know,
something covered in batter and fried to a golden brown.
Hey, wait up, you two! Come back here,
Nezuko! Tanjiro, where are you going?
Wh-what was that for?
Hey, hey! Don't you start chasing us now, too, Inosuke!
Save me, Tanjiro!
All better.
It is north-northeast! To the north-northeast!
Your next mission is north-northeast!
The three of you are to go to Mount
Natagumo! Make your way there posthaste!
We're heading out.
Thank you for everything.
I'll bestow good luck upon you.
We appreciate it.
What do you think you're doing?!
Stop that, you idiot!
What did you say?!
It's ceremonial! We're going on a
journey, and striking sparks is for luck!
Always live your lives in a fashion where
you are able to hold your heads up high.
I wish you luck in battle.
"Heads up high"? "Luck in battle"? What's that mean?
Jeez, this guy is totally clueless.
To be honest, it is a little bit difficult to explain.
"To hold your head high,"
I guess it means, whatever hand you're given in this life,
you're able to conduct yourself in a way that's honorable
so you're never ashamed.
And wishing us luck in battle just
means she's praying for our safety.
Well, what about the "hand you're given"? We
have two already! And why should we be ashamed?
Well, I guess...
What does it mean to conduct yourself honorably, anyway?
And why is that old hag praying
for our safety in the first place?
She has nothing to do with us, so what's her game, huh?
Maybe she should worry about her own hands!
He sped up!
Is this a race? I won't let you win!
Wait for me, you two!
Everyone! We need to pause here.
Zenitsu? What's wrong?
I'm nervous, okay?! Now that we're
nearing our destination, I'm getting scared!
Why the hell is he sitting like
that? It's pretty weird, if you ask me.
Who are you to talk to me about weird?
You can't tell me you're not getting
any spooky vibes from that mountain!
Even so, we can't exactly just wait here.
I told you this guy's an odd duck.
I am not an odd duck! I'm completely
normal! It's you guys that are the strange ones!
Tanjiro? There something wrong?
What is this smell?
Tanjiro! Hey! Wait up! Don't leave me
here by myself! Who knows what'll happen?!
Help me. Please, help me.
Look at his uniform. That boy, he's one of us!
Hey, don't leave me behind!
Are you all right? What happened?
They were attached to me, too!
Please don't let me die here!
I'm going in.
I'll head in first. You stay behind
me, trembling like a scared little animal.
This is making me hungry.
Inosuke.
Why is he such a showoff?
Let's go!
What is this?
A spider web?
This place is full of 'em, as
far as the eye can see! What a pain!
Yeah, you're right.
Inosuke?
What do you want?
I appreciate this.
What?
When you said you'd go check
things out with me, I was relieved.
Huh?
That ominous scent I was picking up from the mountain
scared me a bit, so having you here makes me feel better.
So thanks.
I believe you will find them
comfortable and pleasant to the touch.
Always live your lives in a fashion where
you are able to hold your heads up high.
I wish you luck in battle.
Inosuke.
Let's go.
We've come to help out. I'm Tanjiro Kamado, rank mizunoto.
A mizunoto? You serious?
They should have sent us a Hashira.
No matter how many mizunoto
they send in, it won't be enough!
Inosuke!
Ah, shut up!
The only thing I see around here that's not enough
is this sputtering pool of sweat in front of me!
Now, how 'bout you tell us just what is going on here!
Who do you think you're talking to?
Did you forget that I have seniority?
The crow gave us orders to come to this
place, and ten of us Corps members gathered here.
Not long after we entered the
mountain, that's when it started.
The slayers began killing each other.
I
I was so...
You did well to return.
It would appear that... Most
of my children have been killed.
We may very well find the Twelve Kizuki there.
It would seem I'll have to send in some Hashira.
Giyu...
And Shinobu.
Understood.
If only humans and demons could get along
with each other. Wouldn't you agree, Tomioka?
That's a pipe dream, as long as demons hunt us.
I wonder if the others hate me.
Would someone normally leave
their friend behind like this?
You'd talk him through it if you were close, wouldn't you?
If they both had tried to convince
me to go, I would have. I'm sure of it.
But instead, they both went on their merry way up
that scary mountain, leaving poor, little me all alone.
You don't have a care in the world, do
you? All our human problems, you have no idea.
You think you're being cute right now?! Well, you're
really not! I don't like this side of you one tiny bit!
Why can't you take some notes from Nezuko,
huh?! She's adorable, and she's a Demon!
I just realized he took Nezuko along with him!
Why did he have to go and take my precious
Nezuko with him like that?! Damn you, Tanjiro!
Taking a young girl like her
into danger? Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
I'll save you, Nezuko!
That rattling sound, what is it?
Not again.
Huh?
I've heard this sound before. It's the sound I heard
the moment before everyone started to kill each other.
Where's it coming from?
These guys morons or somethin'?
They don't know that it's taboo for
us Demon slayers to fight each other!
That's not it! They're acting
odd, like they're being manipulated.
Here we go.
I'm gonna cut 'em to pieces!
You can't do that! They're
alive! At least, I believe some are.
Besides, the bodies of the ones
who aren't are still our teammates!
Listen, you. Stop denying me at every turn!
I caught a strange, sweet scent from his back.
It's threads! They're being
controlled by threads! Cut them off!
I already knew about that before you caught on.
Where's the location of the Demon controlling them?
What's that revolting odor? Was just for a second, though.
Spiders?
I get it! The spiders are just attaching
people to the puppet strings. That means...
Now listen closely, my precious little
dolls. Dance until your arms and legs fall off.
Cutting the threads isn't enough. The
spiders will just replace them. So we...
That horrible smell again. What
is it? It's coming from far away.
So all we gotta do is annihilate those damn insects, huh?
No way! They're too small, and there's
gotta be at least a million of them.
We gotta find the Demon who's controlling them instead!
Gotcha!
It's no good, Inosuke. Listen, if you have some
kind of power that can pinpoint the Demon's location,
that would really help!
This disgusting smell has been blowing
in, but I just can't tell where it's from!
You there, your name?!
It's Murata!
Murata, the two of us will take
care of the people being controlled.
In the meantime...
I will not let you disturb my family's peaceful life.
He's floating? No. He's standing on the threads.
His family?
Mother will be sure to make quick work of all of you.
Who's mother?
Damn you!
Where the hell do you think
you're going? Fight me! Fight...
You all right, Inosuke?
Why did he even show up, anyway?
I don't think he's the Demon who's
controlling our people with those threads.
We can't focus on him now.
Okay, okay, okay! I get it, all right?
You want me to go find the one
who is! Shut up about it already!
Beast breathing. Seventh form, spatial awareness!
I've found you, you Demon!
I won't let anyone get in our way.
The five of us are going to live in happiness as a
family. No one on this mortal plane will tear us apart.