Take this! Come on! Move it!
Now, you spineless coward! Draw your sword, and face me!
Fine, then. You leave no choice, but
to take you out along with that box!
Stop it!
I said stop!
Get away!
I heard it! He broke his ribs!
Aren't you part of the demon slayer corps?!
You must understand why Zenitsu refuses to draw his sword,
because it's taboo for us to
fight each other without provocation!
But here you are, giving him
a completely one-sided beating.
Is that fun for you?
You are the lowest of the low!
So that's how you feel? I didn't realize.
In that case, let's fight barehanded.
No! Did you even hear a word I just said?
Listen.
We're not supposed to fight each other in any way!
Using your hands doesn't change
things! Are you listening to me?
Man, look at this guy. How is he able to move like that?
And with some of his ribs broken, no less.
If we're being fair here, Tanjiro's guilty of
going against the rules as well. He broke his bones.
The attacks he's using...
They're unusually low.
The way we're fighting, it's almost like
I'm battling a fearsome, four-legged beast!
Get down, and go for a low blow of
your own. He won't be able to dodge this!
How is he this flexible?! It doesn't even seem human!
What did you think of that move?
Pretty damn amazing, don't you think?
Singing his own praises like that? Give me a break.
Let me demonstrate what else I'm capable of.
Stop it! What are you doing? Performing a stunt
like that in your condition won't be good for you!
So? What do I care?!
Nothing can take away from this
moment and the pleasure I feel!
But you have to think about the future as well!
Why should I?
Now calm down!
Do you hear?!
That sound! Did both of your skulls get fractured?!
Huh?! Are you kidding me! That's what you look like?!
What the hell are you saying?
You got a problem with my face or something?
I don't know what to make of you right now. You've got
this ripped body, but such a delicate face to go with it.
What? Why are you obsessed with my face all of a sudden?
No! I-I'm not! It was just an observation!
There's nothing wrong with your face.
In fact, the girlish shape, size,
and complexion are quite attractive!
You're a dead man! You wanna go?
I don't! I won't fight you anymore.
Come on. Head-butt me!
No! I'm done!
I said do it!
You're too worked up. Why don't you just sit down?
I got a better idea! How about I tell you my name?
It's Inosuke Hashibira. Don't you forget it!
How is that spelled, exactly?
Huh? I, I don't know how to read and write, okay?
All I know is that name was written on my...
Huh? What's wrong?
Guess he froze.
What's the matter?
Oh, no! He collapsed!
Is he dead?
No, he's not. I think it's a concussion.
I did head-butt him really hard, though.
But are you all right, Tanjiro?
Yeah.
Amazing! Can I touch your head?
Sure.
That's insane. There's not a single drop of blood
from Tanjiro's head. How hard could it possibly be?
I mean, look at what it did to him.
Tanjiro, your head is so hard!
You think so?
He's awake!
Fight me! Fight me now! Get back here, you!
I can't believe this is how
he acts right when he wakes up!
What are you up to? Tell me!
We're having a burial.
Burial?
Yes, and you should help out, too.
The fact of the matter is lives were lost in there.
What's the point in putting things
that have died into the ground like that?
I'm not doing that, not on your life!
Forget that crap! Let's finish our fight!
This guy's cold. Did he really just
ask what the point in burying people was?
I understand.
You can't do it, because you're in too much pain.
I thought it was just the boar
guy, but they're both crazy.
Hey, it's all right. Everyone handles
their pain threshold differently, you know.
Moving those who died outside the mansion and then
digging graves for their bodies is extremely hard work.
Zenitsu, these kids, and I will
do our best, so don't you worry!
He's so odd.
Strange guy.
You should get some rest, Inosuke.
Sorry to ask too much of you.
Don't underestimate me, damn
it! I can Bury 100, no, 200 bodies!
I'm gonna do way more work than any of you! Just watch!
What's that strange man doing?
Just look the other way.
Descend the mountain! Descend the mountain!
Is that crow talking to us?
This is all a bit too much.
Yeah.
All right, everyone! It's time to follow yours truly!
Hey! Where are you going?
We're descending the mountain.
But we're not done with our battle yet.
You're tired, aren't you? Come on. We're heading down.
What?! I'm not tired at all!
Let's fight!
No, you can't! I won't allow it!
Don't go, Shoichi! Please, you gotta
stay with us! I've seen how powerful you are!
I need you around to protect me from danger!
Stop it! He's obviously not interested!
Don't leave me behind, Shoichi! I beg you!
Stop that this instant!
Hold out your hands!
That will ward off demons. As the one with
Marechi, be sure to keep that on your person.
It smells like Wisteria.
What's that?
A flower demons can't stand. Make sure not to lose it.
It's a demon repellent. It will keep them at bay.
Tanjiro, thank you for everything.
We can all get home on our own now.
Safe travels.
Now, everyone, follow me! Follow yours truly!
Come on, and fight me! I swear I'm gonna
find your weak point and bring you down!
I have a name, you know. It's Tanjiro Kamado!
All right, Gonpachiro Kamaboko, I'm gonna bring you down!
Who are you talking about?
You, of course!
No, you're not!
'Scuse me! Could you keep it down, please?!
A Wisteria family crest.
It's time to rest! It's time to rest!
You've all had a tough day! Rest up now!
Are you sure that's okay?
Now that you mention it, I have been
fighting with injuries this whole time.
Is that a laugh or...
Let's eat this thing.
What?
Yes?
Oh. Sorry to bother you this late at night.
A ghost! It's a ghost!
Quiet!
Who the hell are you?
Should I presume that you are all demon slayers?
We are. What's it to you?
Inosuke!
Please come in.
That little old lady sure walks fast.
This is where you'll be staying.
A change of clothes to cleanse your body.
And a warm meal to cleanse your soul.
She has to be a monster! Preparing all this so
quickly? There's no way she's human! She can't be!
She's a monster grandm...
Use your chopsticks.
If you're really that hungry, Inosuke, have this bowl too.
Take it.
I refuse!
Is this moron for real?
He's forgotten all about the box that was
so important to him earlier. Give me a break!
Your bedding is ready, gentlemen.
Again! The monst...
I'm takin' this one here.
First come, first serve!
That's fine. You can sleep wherever you want.
Which one do you want, Zenitsu?
Why me?!
Our doctor is ready to see you.
Greetings.
Yes, I see.
Well, it's bad.
Who would have guessed? All three of us have broken ribs.
This bump, though, hurts a lot more.
Sorry.
'Scuse me. Where's my apology? I'm hurting, too.
You beat the crap out of me earlier. You sorry?
Not really.
Just apologize!
Forget it.
Hey, be nice.
Look, Inosuke, we just won't
eat with you if you act that way.
How's that related?
Because meals always taste better
when you eat together, you know?
Yeah, he's right.
Did the two of you hit your heads or something?
Like you're one to talk about that!
Do you need any assistance in there?
Ahh! The monster!
Stop that!
According to what the crow told me,
this house with the Wisteria family crest
belongs to a family that was
once rescued by demon slayers.
That's the reason they're housing us free of charge here.
Still, I didn't think they
would show us this much kindness.
Pays to be with the demon slayer corps, huh?
Now that I think about it, what
made you decide to join the group?
Well, you must have had some kind of reason.
A member of the demon slayer
corps barged in on me on my mountain,
so we competed to see who was
stronger. I took his blade as a reward.
I feel sorry for that guy.
And then I heard of this thing called "final
selection" and the fact that demons really do exist.
So that's what drew you to the demon slayer corps.
And, hey, you grew up in the mountains. Same goes for me.
Don't lump me in with you! I don't
have anyone I could call family.
Only one thing gives me comfort in this world,
and that's testing my strength against others!
Is that so? How sad.
Hey, Tanjiro, there's something
I've been meaning to ask you.
You're traveling with a demon. What is that about?
Zenitsu, you knew, and you still protected the box.
You really are a good person. You know that?
Thank you.
You don't have to compliment me like that.
I've got a keen sense of smell.
That's how I knew from the start.
You're a kind person, Zenitsu, strong, too.
Hey, I'm not that strong. Give me a break.
That's why I wanted to bring Shoichi
along with us, but you ruined it.
Uh, but I... That's... well...
Wh-what's happening?! Is it coming after us now?
You don't have to worry.
How can you be so sure?! How?! How?!
Quiet down. It's the middle of the night, Zenitsu.
Why won't he take the bait? I
took his food and everything.
Come to think of it, what exactly was
it that got him so mad before? I forget.
It's not even locked?! You're kidding me?!
Shh!
P-p-protect me!
Someone please protect me!
Even you'll do, Inosuke!
Stay away from me!
It's escaped!
I-I gotta hide! I'm so scared!
Hey, Nezuko.
That's enough activity for one day.
I'll introduce you. Nezuko is my...
Tanjiro.
You didn't.
Hey, what's wrong?
Tell me you didn't.
Just who do you think you are?
You've been traveling with a girl... This adorable?
Hanging around with someone this cute day in and day out
and been having a great time in the process, haven't you?
Wait a minute. That's not...
Well, then, why did I bear all that pain and suffering?!
Tanjiro, you jerk! You getting to be all, "ooh," and,
"mwah," with a cutie is not what I was toiling away for!
I did not put myself in harm's way to get
pummeled and kicked around by a crazy boar guy!
Zenitsu, calm down! What has gotten into you?
Did you think I joined the demon slayer corps because
I thought it was gonna be all sunshine and rainbows?
Well, I...
Guys like you should be erased
from this world immediately!
I will finally make you pay for thwarting my marriage,
as well as sending my savior and protector Shoichi home.
You shall face justice! Don't ever disrespect the corps!
You fiend! How could you!
Zenitsu, cut it out!
Mock the demon slayers corps, and you'll get
sent straight to hell! You shall feel my wrath!