South-southeast!
The next place you need to go is south-southeast!
I heard you!
You don't have to keep squawking it at me, okay?
I'm begging you! I got the message, so be quiet!
Please!
Please! Please! Please!
Please marry me!
You know I could die any day now!
Marry me so I don't die alone!
Marry me! I'm begging you, please!
Wh-what is he doing?
What on earth?
Uh, yes?
Come on! I'm begging you!
There's no one else!
You're the only hope that I have left!
So that's it, then.
Okay, I'll try to help.
Please! I'm asking you again! Marry me! I beg you!
Why are you making such a scene in the middle of the road?
She's clearly not interested in you!
Also, you're stressing your sparrow out!
Wait. That uniform.
Aren't you that guy from final selection?
Don't go pretending like we know
each other, cause we don't, 'kay?!
Huh?! But we have met!
Don't you remember?! Don't get angry at me
when you're the one with the terrible memory!
All right. You're all set to head home again.
Do you need help with anything else?
No. Thank you very much.
Hang on!
Don't you interfere!
That girl is madly in love with me!
The two of us are gonna get marrie...
Aah! Hey! Ouch! That hurts!
Aah! Aah! Stop! Ow! Ow!
Hey, calm down!
When did I say anything even resembling that I loved you?!
All I did was come talk to you while you were crumpled up
all disheveled on the side of the road!
Huh?! No!
So are you telling me the reason you did that
wasn't because you were falling in love with me?
Considering that I already have a fiance,
that's exactly what I've been trying to tell you!
Well, you seem to be perfectly fine now, so goodbye!
W-wait! Come back! Please...
Would you give it a rest already?
Wh-why did you have to get in my way?
This had nothing to do with you.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Stop it! You're staring at me like I'm
some sort of pitiful creature or something!
Now listen here, you! The reason I missed
out on getting married is all your fault!
Say something, would you?!
Look, during my next job, I'll likely die.
The reason is I'm just a weakling. Do you understand?
You have to help protect me until
I manage to get married, mister.
My name's Tanjiro. And you are?
Tanjiro? That's good to know.
I'm Zenitsu Agatsuma.
Please, you've gotta do what you can to save me.
Aren't you being a bit dramatic?
Why did you even become a swordsman?
You're acting utterly pathetic right now.
That's a harsh way to put it!
I got conned by a woman and racked up a lot of debt!
The old geezer who took it over for me
happened to be this tough-as-nails instructor!
He made me train to the bone every day!
It was so hellish, I just wanted to die!
I was hoping that'd happen during final selection!
But, since I survived, this
nightmare continues to haunt me!
Agh! I'm so scared, terrified, frightened!
I just know I'm gonna get eaten by a demon soon!
My brains are gonna get sucked
through my ears while I'm still alive!
Yaaah!
No!
Please save me!
Hey, are you okay?
You better?
A bit, but now I'm feeling really hungry.
Don't you have any food or rations on you?
No.
Here. Take one of these.
Really?
Thank you so much.
Aren't you gonna eat anything?
Um, that was all I had.
Hey, uh, you take this half.
You sure about that? Thanks a lot.
I know what you mean when you
say that you're terrified of demons,
but you should try not to worry your sparrow.
Hah?
You're saying it was distressed? How could you tell?
Let's see. He says you're always
whining about not wanting to go to work,
and you're always hitting on
girls, and you snore really loudly.
Yup, that covers it.
Wait. He said all that?
You can understand bird language?
Yeah.
No way! You've gotta be lying to me!
Start running! Start running!
Run, Tanjiro! Run, Zenitsu!
Both of you must head to your next destination!
That crow is talking to us!
Hey, Tanjiro, maybe I should just hang back for now.
Even if I tag along with you, I'm
not gonna be able to do anything.
The scent of demons is getting stronger.
There's something up ahead.
A house?
I can smell blood, but it's strange.
Wait. You can smell something here?
Yeah, but this is a whole new smell.
A smell? I can't say I'm getting that.
What about that sound? You're able to hear that, right?
Sound?
There are kids here?
They look scared.
Hey, there.
Is there a reason you're out here by yourselves?
They're definitely terrified.
Guess what. I have got something really cool here.
Wanna see it?
Ta-da!
It's a friendly sparrow.
See? Isn't he cute?
Talk to me. Did something happen?
Is this your house?
No. No, it's not.
This is... this house is...
It... it belongs to a...
Monster.
Our big brother got taken away.
We were walking down the road at night,
and this thing appeared in front of us.
It went straight for our
brother, never giving us a glance.
Did it take him into that house?
Yeah. That's right.
So you two followed them here?
That's real brave. Great job.
We used the traces of his blood to follow them.
That thing really hurt him.
I see.
It'll be all right.
We're gonna go defeat the bad guy
and save your brother.
Is that true? You'll help him?
Yes. I promise.
Hey, Tanjiro.
Huh?
Uh, what is that strange sound?
It's really unnerving and never stops.
It sounds like a drum.
A drum?
I don't hear anything.
Just cover your eyes!
Are you all right?
Can you hear me? Just hang on!
This is bad. The wound is so deep.
Even though I was able to...
escape from that horrible place, and make it here...
was it not enough?
Am I still gonna die?
He's gone.
I'm sorry you had to suffer like that.
Tanjiro...
By any chance, would that happen to be these kids'...
We couldn't save him.
If we'd only gotten here a little sooner,
things might have been different.
Uh, hey, is this your brother?
No.
No, that isn't him.
He was wearing an orange-colored kimono.
I see.
So it's captured more than one person.
I promise to bury you once I return.
Until then, please forgive me.
All right. Zenitsu, let's go!
Look, the only people who can help them
are you and me now.
All right, then. Have it your way.
Hey! Tanjiro, don't be so scary!
Fine! I give in! You win! I'll come along with you, okay?!
Don't let me force you.
I said I'll go!
In case you run into trouble, I'm leaving this box.
If you need help, it'll protect you.
Okay. We'll be back.
So, Tanjiro,
hey, before we continue,
whatever's in this place with us,
you'll be sure to protect me from it, won't you?
Zenitsu,
I hate to have to tell you this, but, in my last fight,
I broke a leg and a rib.
Neither of them have fully healed up as of yet, so...
Wait! What?! You have broken bones?!
What do you think you're trying to do to me?!
If you're in that condition, my fate has been sealed!
I'm gonna d-d-d-die!
This is awful! What am I gonna do? I'm finished!
It's all over for me! Yaah!
I can't believe you have broken bones!
I'm a dead man now, completely and utterly dead!
I'm dead! I'm dead...
Zenitsu, you've gotta calm down. You'll be all right.
Don't feed me your empty promises!
No, it's true. You're gonna be fine, because you're...
Stay away!
You two shouldn't be here!
W-we're sorry.
There were sounds coming from inside that box.
Still, I really wish you hadn't left it behind.
That thing is more precious to me than my own life.
Oops! Sorry.
The room changed.
Or could it be that we somehow
moved during the beat of that drum?
Sorry you got separated from your brother,
but I'm gonna protect you, no matter what.
And Zenitsu is going to protect your brother. Don't worry.
What's your name?
It's Teruko.
Your name's Teruko?
Your parents picked out a really...
Among all the different scents in this mansion,
this is the strongest one.
It's eaten so many.
This one has to be the master of this place.
I'm gonna die!
It's over! It's over! It's
over! It's over! I just know it!
I can't believe Tanjiro and I got separated!
Teruko, you here?
It's Shoichi!
Hey, hey, hey!
You can't go around yelling like that!
If the bad guy hears you and finds us,
it's not gonna be pretty! Let's just go wait outside!
Hah?
Why would we do that?
Are you trying to escape all by yourself?
All this constant whining about dying,
aren't you a little ashamed?
It's pathetic that you're clinging to the
sleeve of someone who's younger than you.
Why does a coward like you have a
sword on your hip in the first place?
Those words... They cut me right to my core.
Listen here, you! I'm not gonna be useful here, anyway...
So I'm just gonna go find an adult who can help us, okay?
This isn't something us kids can resolve on our own.
No way! You've gotta be kidding me!
How's this not the front door?!
Did I misremember? I was sure it was here!
This one?
Maybe here!
Or here!
It's a monster!
What the heck?! What's with that look?! S-Stop it!
If it hadn't been for them,
if it hadn't been for them and their meddling...
Teruko...
You gotta try not to scream.
The room might change again, so don't go far, all right?
Go hide behind those shelves.
Curses. Curses!
Thanks to them, he was able to get away.
That prey was mine and mine alone.
Damn them. Why do all these unwelcome
guests keep barging into someone else's home?
It's maddening.
That prey belonged to me.
I found it with my own two hands on my own property.
Those filthy rats.
I'll make them pay.
Hey, you, listen up!
I'm a demon slayer, rank mizunoto, Tanjiro Kamado!
It's my duty to slay you now!
A child with Marechi that I found myself!
Got him.
Teruko!
I thought this might happen.
The room's been flipped.
So this is his blood demon art.
This entire mansion is his territory.
What's this?
There's an odd scent, but it's not a demon.
Better watch out, 'cause, ready or not,
here I come!
Who is this guy?
He's wearing a boar's hide.
And he's wielding nichirin swords.
All right, you monster,
die on the battlefield, and serve as my catalyst
so that I may become even more
powerful and soar to new heights!
Infuriating.
Just infuriating!
Hope you're ready for me,
'cause I'm comin' through!