[CHUCHU]
So, what do you think, Cyan?
Huh? I'm not really sure.
Wait! I've got an idea!
What do you think
about this progression?
[CHUCHU]
Yeah, that could work!
They may have lost
the Battle of the Bands,
but they seem to be headed
in the right direction now.
Look how driven they are!
[MAPLE chuckles]
You can say that again!
Things are slowly but
surely moving along.
And the girls seem to be
growing closer, as well.
Nice one!
All right, why don't
we call it a day?
Let's work on our own
parts at home and then
put 'em all together again
at practice tomorrow!
[CYAN]
Sounds good to me!
[MOA]
Okay! Let's do it!
Excuse me, I--
[CYAN, MOA, CHUCHU]
Huh?
So, after tomorrow's practice,
maybe we...
What is it? Go on.
I was, wondering if
you wanted to join me.
[CHUCHU]
Are those tickets?
[CYAN] T-Tozen Naru Kuri-kiri
Mabo-roshi no An?
I know the font's weird,
but it's "Tsurezurenaru
Ayatsuri Mugenan"!
"Tsurezure"?
So, yeah. If you're interested,
I thought maybe we
could all go together
and see their concert.
I've heard of them! They're
super popular right now.
Of course I'm
interested! Thank you!
[whimpering]
[MOA] I'm so stoked to go
to a Tsurezure concert
that I might just explode!
Retoree! Thank you so much!
[DAGGER]
I see. So she's at BRR?
[OGASAWARA]
Yes, sir.
[DAGGER]
Has Maple noticed as of yet?
[OGASAWARA] No, sir. Thus far,
it doesn't appear so.
[DAGGER]
And?
[OGASAWARA]
Well, Plasmagica wasn't bad.
They sounded all right.
But, honestly, they don't even
hold a candle to Criticris--
[DAGGER]
I don't care about the band!
I want to know more
about the new girl.
The guitar player.
[OGASAWARA]
Of course! Forgive me, sir!
The rumors are true.
I don't know what it is,
but there's definitely something
about that girl named Cyan.
[DAGGER]
I see.
It appears my hunch
about her was correct.
Cyan, huh?
One way or another, someday
soon, she'll end up here.
I must have her lead the
best band in Sound World
and stand at the very top.
[OGASAWARA]
So, what should I do about her?
[DAGGER] Let her swim
along a little longer.
The higher she raises
her musical skills,
the better it will be for us.
Keep a watchful eye.
[OGASAWARA]
Yes, sir!
[gasping] It's almost time for
the Tsurezure awesome-show!
Wow, Moa, you like
'em that much?
I'm gonna explode!
While we're having
fun at their concert,
might as well try to find out
the secret to their popularity.
Wow, I guess they
really are well-known,
aren't they? What kind of
music do they play anyway?
No way!
Cyan, do you really not
know who Tsurezure are?
[gasps] Uh...
No...
[CHUCHU] Cyan. Where you're
from is still a mystery,
and you'd never heard of Saint
Midi Girls' Academy, either.
What have you been doing
with your life up till now?
[A]
All right.
Let's use today's performance
to continue our training.
[UN]
For sure!
After all, spreading music from
the Far East to Midi City
is the perfect opportunity
to do so, right?
[DARUDAYU]
Yes, girls. That's the spirit.
[A]
Master!
It must have been fate
that led us to meet a master
such as you. One from the
Far East of our birth.
To think we're able to
study under the tutelage
of someone as virtuous
as you, Master!
We're so very grateful!
[DARUDAYU]
Now, now.
While I appreciate the praise,
you girls are not that
much younger than I.
You should not depend on me
to the extent that you do.
Please, Master.
You are far too humble.
With your virtue and skill
at playing the drum,
surely you can teach us
what music really is.
We eagerly await your
continued guidance.
[DARUDAYU]
Oh, my!
I do admire your spirit!
Now, let us go.
[A, UN]
Master!
[CROWD cheering]
It's finally time!
[A, UN]
♪ It's begun! ♪
[DARUDAYU]
♪ The journey starts. ♪
[A, UN]
♪ Ah... Ah... ♪
[A]
Tsurezurenaru Ayatsuri Mugenan!
[UN] We have journeyed
from distant lands
to bring you the
sounds of our home.
The Far East!
[A]
I am the one known as "A"!
[UN]
And I am the one known as "Un"!
[A] We are honored to share
the stage with our leader
in all things.
Master Darudayu!
[DARUDAYU] My thanks for
the kind introduction.
[DARUDAYU] It will bring
me great pleasure
for you to thoroughly
enjoy our sound tonight.
[CROWD cheering]
[DARUDAYU]
♪ See the blooming ♪
♪ of wonderful
fireworks above. ♪
♪ Here the train blow its
whistle in the night. ♪
[A] ♪ Oh, my heart,
it beats so uneasily ♪
♪ in the dryness of
a sleepless night. ♪
♪ Apprehension hangs
in the air, ♪
♪ so I respond with
one step forward. ♪
[UN]
♪ Shining in the sky, ♪
♪ the Milkyway is kissing
me with countless dreams ♪
♪ and wishes.
Idol thoughts change ♪
♪ incessantly, they search
for a new path to start. ♪
[DARUDAYU, A]
♪ It's begun. ♪
[UN]
♪ So, the journey begins. ♪
[DARUDAYU, A, UN]
♪ The blinking sky reveals ♪
♪ blooming fireworks
of dreams. ♪
♪ On our journey, we may
find a single path to tread. ♪
♪ Choices swirling like
cherry blossoms all around. ♪
♪ A kaleidoscope, dazzling
and confounding to see. ♪
[CROWD cheering]
[whimpering]
[CHUCHU] Their ability is
just-- It's truly amazing!
[RETOREE]
I can't even.
[CROWD cheers]
[CYAN] Not only is their skill
and playing impressive,
but the way that they
work the crowd is, too!
Wow.
[A] Master. I was wondering
what you thought
of tonight's performance.
I feel that the audience
seemed to really enjoy us,
judging by their enthusiasm.
[BOTH gasp]
What is it? Don't you
think it went well?
[sighs] My, my, you girls
still have a long way to go.
[A, UN gasp]
Although they liked us,
it does not mean we
were "good enough"!
[BOTH]
What? But why?
Please consider
the circumstance.
Was not today the
first time we performed
here in Shibu Valley?
[A]
Yes, Master.
We can safely assume,
there's a high probability
the audience merely found
Far Eastern music curious.
[BOTH gasp]
If you mistake such enthusiasm
for our own abilities,
then you've simply proven
your level of inexperience.
Yes! Obviously!
We were so blind.
We have not trained
nearly enough.
You must be ever diligent
to walk the path
of the performing arts.
Work hard! Don't give up!
[BOTH]
Master!
I'm pleased you see
how things are.
Now, then.
Since we came all the
way to Shibu Valley,
the town of young people...
[A]
Yes?
[DARUDAYU] Why don't we
enjoy ourselves a little?
[A, UN]
We were hoping for that!
It's so yummy!
Tsurezure really have a lot
of spirit, don't they?
Sure do!
Their costumes, their
performance, their songs--
Everything was just
bursting with uniqueness!
[MOA sighs]
You okay?
[MOA]
Oh! Uh.
[laughs] They were
amazing is all!
Looks like you
were so blown away
that everything's just
goin' in one ear
and out the other one, huh?
[MOA]
Heh, maybe.
Hey, those girls are our rivals!
You can't just think of 'em
with a fan's point of view.
That's a good point, Retoree.
No time to sit back
and bask in their glow.
We need to figure out
a way to raise the bar
of our performances
up to their level.
[sighs] Maybe, people like
their originality.
You might be on
to something there.
Heh. Although, the giant
Dharma Doll was a tad much,
dontcha think?
[yelps]
Chuchu, hey, what's wrong?
Uh--!
[MOA, CYAN]
Huh?
[ALL yelp]
So it looks like they
have those "pancakes"
everyone's been
talking about here.
[A]
Yum.
I can't decide if I want that
or everything else on the menu!
[UN giggles]
I know! Me, either!
What should we do?
[MOA, CYAN, CHUCHU gasp]
[whispering] Retoree, wait!
What are you doing?
I wanted...
[DARUDAYU]
Hm?
[gasps] She's not gonna
make a rival declaration?
We're not ready for
something like that!
Retoree! Don't do it!
I just... wanna say...
[RETOREE]
I am such a huge fan!
[ALL]
Huh?
Why, thank you, it's so very
nice of you to say that!
Thank you! I support
everything you do!
Um. Excuse me!
Yes, dear?
Moa?
Huh?
Wha--?
Your lyrics based
on the Far East...
They've touched me in
ways I can't describe!
Is that so?
Are you far from
your home, as well?
[yelps]
[DARUDAYU chuckles]
It's no wonder.
Your hometown is something
carved into your heart.
You carry it with you forever.
No matter how far away
you are or where it is.
[gasps]
By the way, who are you girls?
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[DARUDAYU]
Don't tell me...
[CYAN]
Our originality?
That's right.
I suppose we should start
with the way we look.
You really think so?
Just what are you getting at?
We should wear our originality.
[CYAN, CHUCHU, MOA]
Huh?
Or, to put it another way,
I think we should
all wear battle armor.
Muah! How's this, sugar?
I dunno. It might be
a little too much?
So. Whatcha think?
[RETOREE]
Meh. Kinda cliché.
[MOA whines]
Meow!
[MOA]
That doesn't go with our songs.
[CHUCHU]
Not so much.
[cackles]
[CHUCHU] We need to have
a serious talk, Moa. And no.
I, uh...
[gasps]
[cackles]
[CHUCHU]
We are so getting nowhere.
It's hard to choose.
Which one do you guys
think works best?
[AION, YAIBA, CROW]
Uh--!
[CROW]
Oh, we weren't looking!
What are you talking about?
[CHUCHU] I was asking about
our performance outfits.
[CROW]
How should I know?
[YAIBA] As for myself,
even if you were clad in rags
from head to toe,
my Ryukenden would remain
true and pure. Hence--
[AION] It is proof you
are ignorant people
who go against god if your
hearts are wicked enough
to be tempted by
costumes like that.
If you have reached
the divine realm of god,
even if you were not wearing
a thread of clothing,
you would be able to reach
the hearts of the audience!
What are you bozos doing?
You're so noisy.
Rom! Hey! Perfect
timing, as always!
I was hopin' you could tell us
your opinion on somethin'.
On what? I'm tired
today, for real.
Keep it simple.
Curry for me, thank you!
[ANGELICA]
You got it.
We wanted to try showcasing
our personalities
and creativity on stage
by wearing a uniform.
But we're having trouble
choosing, so which one
do you think best suits us?
[cackles]
Hold on a second.
I think you guys are
misunderstanding something.
[CHUCHU]
Huh?
What kinda clothes you
wear doesn't determine
if your band is any good.
All you can do is fight the
good fight and bare your soul
with everything you've got.
I know, but yesterday,
we all went to see
this unique band in
concert who's recently
become really popular.
And we've been thinkin' that
maybe it'd help our popularity
if we showed more--
It's not just about
being popular!
[CHUCHU gasps]
[gasps]
Later. Tomorrow comes early.
Hold up, Rom!
You're leaving already?
[ROM]
Sorry. I said too much.
[MOA, CYAN, RETOREE sigh]
I'm sorry.
I might've gone too far
with my own personal taste.
'S okay.
I got pretty caught up in it,
too. No apology needed.
So then, uh, could I
change now, please? Meow?
[CHUCHU, RETOREE, MOA chuckle]
[CROWD cheering]
Hey! Long time, no see, old pal.
Not long enough.
And is it really
a good idea for you
to be hangin' around here?
Star like you
could cause a riot.
I didn't get a chance
to properly thank you
for the other day.
So, thanks for warming
up the crowd for us!
It helped make me
shine all the more!
What a shame. You
haven't changed at all.
[SHUZO]
I'm waiting for you.
Aren't you gonna even
try to get on my level?
You bastard!
[CROWD cheering]
Damn. Guess you haven't
gotten soft at least.
You know what--
[CROW]
Yo! Hey, Rom! Wait up!
It's my band-mates.
See ya! Bye, Rom!
[CROW] Hm? Who was that?
Somebody you know?
No, not really.
So anyway, what are
you guys doin' here?
[laughs] Well, we were
thinking about gettin'
some ramen, man. Wanna join?
Wait a sec.
Didn't you guys just have
curry back at the café?
So what?
That kind of curry
is a drink, idiot!
Ramen is known as the
Legend of the Favorite Plate,
as they say. So, hence--
[AION] The matter in question
is carved in the book
of the Dark Apocalypse.
It is not a prank of the rodent.
Looks like I've got no choice!
Let's go.
I guess the guy with a job
will treat you this time.
[CROW, YAIBA, AION chuckle]
[CROW] That's our Rom!
Yo, wait up! Hey!
[CHUCHU] Honestly, I think
what Rom was saying
makes perfect sense.
[RETOREE]
Agreed.
I don't think we should
start with how we look.
We should win everyone over
with our musicianship.
Yeah, that's a good point.
When they perform,
Tsurezure really know
how to present themselves.
And outwardly, that presentation
looks very original.
But nobody can do
what they can do.
It's more about their
music than anything else,
wouldn't you agree?
Yeah, I'd say you hit
a bull's-eye with that one.
It's that Far East sound.
There's so much honesty and
love in what they're singing
because of the love they
have for their hometown.
Their beautiful lyrics hit me
smack dab in the heart!
Oh, hold on!
There's somethin' important
I just remembered!
[RETOREE, CYAN, MOA]
Huh?
We haven't really taken
any time sit down
and write a new song
since Cyan joined us,
know what I mean?
[RETOREE]
Yeah, that's true.
I think it's high time
we changed that!
A new song? Wow!
[giggles]
Heck yes! Sounds good to me!
Me, too! I can't wait
to hear it, pyruu!
[CHUCHU]
That settles it then.
Let's all come up with some
new ideas before the next time
we practice, okay?
[CYAN panting]
He's gonna yell at me.
How could I leave Mister Berry
in the studio like that?
Sorry!
[door clicks]
[MAPLE]
Huh?
Huh? Mister President?
What are you doing down here
at this time of night?
[MAPLE] Oh, uh, just my usual
patrolling, that's all.
Cyan, are you here to do
some individual practice?
Oh, that's so admirable!
What gumption you have!
Oh, Cyan!
Yes, sir?
[MAPLE] This might be a bit
of an awkward question,
but during the
Battle of the Bands,
did Ogasawara from
the other band's agency
say anything to you?
Anything of note?
No, not really.
But I dunno what
"anything of note" means.
[MAPLE] Oh, if he didn't,
then it's fine.
Just fine. Well,
goodnight, then!
Huh? And a goodnight
to you, too!
[CROW] ♪ A sacred miracle
forced to be hidden away ♪
♪ beneath stardust so
cursed that it's light, ♪
♪ turned to black. ♪
Ha, ha! Crow has arrived!
[AION] ♪ Fragrant in darkness,
eternally darkness, ♪
♪ the forbidden darkness,
it calls out the name-- ♪
♪ Devil's sigh. ♪
Breath breaker, Aion!
[YAIBA] ♪ He's so powerful,
he manages to tame ♪
♪ the angry lake of hell fire. ♪
♪ That is the Legend
of Tongue Flame. ♪
Hence, Yaiba appears bearing
his legendary Dragon Sword!
[ROM]
♪ Needs of grown men-- ♪
Fatty oils are a
necessity for men.
♪ Righteousness shines
in lubricant form. ♪
♪ For my name is Rom! ♪
[CROW, AION, YAIBA, ROM]
♪ Sing on your knees, ♪
♪ all of you cattle. ♪
♪ Be baptized in our crimson. ♪
♪ Through your harmony,
taste will be made. ♪
♪ Tonkatsu Ramen!
Tonkatsu Ramen! ♪
[MAPLE]
Go home!
Mama.
[beeping]
[gasps] Wow, it's from Mama!
"Moa. Are you doing well?"
"Are you eating properly?"
Mama.
That makes me really want
a plate of your cooking.
[MOA'S MOM] I'm waiting
anxiously for you to finish
your mission and come home.
Soon, I hope. I miss you dearly.
Until then, work hard
and don't get sick.
Be good.
P.S.
--I thought you might
be having a hard time
with all of the
unfamiliar food there,
so I sent your favorite,
nago-nago fassa-gua,
by regular post.
Boil it, fry it, or steam
it before you eat it.
But, you absolutely
cannot eat it raw.
You must make sure
you cook it first.
With love, from Mama.
Mama!
I hope to go home
and see you soon, too!
Then again...
I've made friends.
And I've become attached to
the music of this planet, too.
I'd miss it.
Creating music makes
me really happy,
and it's fun making
it with friends.
It's strange, but the
girls in the band
make me forget I'm lonely.
They're special, and I don't
wanna leave 'em just yet!
[MOA] I wanna go home,
but I don't wanna go home.
Know what I mean?
[MAPLE]
Oh, my, my!
I feel trouble a'brewing
for the next episode!
[RETOREE] Don't tell me
BRR is going under?
[MAPLE]
Not at all.
[RETOREE] Well, then is
Angelica leaving the company
to get married?
[MAPLE] What? Wow,
that would be a problem!
What should I do?
[RETOREE]
I made that up.
[MAPLE]
I hate you.