[rumbling]
[UN grunts]
[A grunts]
[DARUDAYU grunts]
[CROWD murmuring]
[MONSTER 5A growls]
[A]
Master!
[UN]
Please be careful!
[DARUDAYU] You will not
disrupt this concert.
'Tis a hideous
desecration of music!
[roars]
[CROWD murmuring]
[MAPLE]
Hey, listen, kids!
I forgot to tell you all
something important
that came up.
You have a mind like
a sieve, President.
[MAPLE] E-heh! You'll all be
performing at next week's
Futures Indies Band concert!
Which means, you gotta get into
fighting shape in a jiffy!
Say what?
That's extreme,
on the real, boss man!
What kind of concert
is it, exactly?
[MAPLE] It's a competition
and talent showcase
for up-and-coming bands,
and a major event!
This thing was practically
made for you guys!
It's a great opportunity!
So go kill it!
As if we wouldn't!
I'm down for that, for sure!
It sounds really fun!
You bet it does, cupcake!
We're gonna be the brightest
of the bright, pyruu!
[CHUCHU, CYAN, RETOREE giggle]
[phone chimes]
[gasps] Hey, guys!
It says the members of
Tsurezure were attacked
by a dark monster!
--[CYAN, CHUCHU, MOA gasp]
--[MAPLE] Huh?
[RETOREE] It looks like
they escaped somehow,
but Darudayu was
actually injured.
No, that's not okay!
Oh, wait. But it doesn't
seem too serious.
Thank you, our lucky stars.
First Trichronika gets hit,
and now Tsurezure, too?
They're going after all
the most famous bands.
[gasps] Get ready, boys.
That probably means
we're next in line!
But it doesn't really matter.
Either way, I'll knock 'em
dead in seconds flat
with my Natural Born
Crimson Knuckles, man!
[AION] It's hilarious to
think the monsters would
even notice someone
so minuscule.
Much less attack him.
Oh, yeah?
You want me to test drive
'em on you first, smart guy?
[YAIBA]
Hmph, it seems time...
[gasps] Hang on a minute.
The day we first
made your acquaintance--
Wasn't that you who drove off
the dark monster, Cyan?
[gasps] Uhhh, that...
was only a...
I kinda got caught up in it,
without really knowing
what was going on.
Then, it just sort of happened?
[CYAN]
Um. Yeah.
If you say so.
[CHUCHU] That's not how
it looked to me, sweetie.
[CHUCHU] For the next show,
I had a major itch
to add a new song to the
playlist, but no matter
how you slice it, we just
don't have enough time.
Dang, you're right.
We only have about ten days.
Hey, Cyan, could
you help me with
a new arrangement for one
of our other songs again?
Sure! I'd love to!
[CHUCHU]
Well, my sugars, goodnight.
See you bright n' early!
Yeah, g'night.
Night-night, sleep tight!
Goodnight, you guys!
[RETOREE]
Cyan?
I thought...
I thought I'd look into the
dark monsters a little bit more,
'cause I'm kinda curious.
If you want to, you can
help me out with it.
I wouldn't mind some
company for a while.
Yeah? Can I?
[CYAN]
What are these?
They're all my computers.
So, you know what every one
of these buttons does?
Crazy. You're using all of them.
We can see what's going
on at different venues
on this screen.
[RETOREE] Bummer. No one's
playing tonight.
Anyway, you can see some
hot new bands over here.
[CYAN]
Cool!
[RETOREE]
And, this is the hits chart.
Tsurezure. Trichronika...
There's Criticrista!
Yeah, I know, they're
getting ultra-popular
these days. Dumb
middle schoolers.
These are forums where people
talk about their favorite bands.
[CYAN]
Really?
Hey, look, there was
something written about you.
What? No kidding?
[RETOREE]
See, it's here.
"The girl who defeated
the dark monster during
Trichronika's concert
looks exactly like Cyan,
who's also the newest
member of Plasmagica.
Her performance was wicked cool,
and her guitar solo
was the ultimate!"
Rad, huh?
Whew. Oh, gosh, I'm
happy! That's so cool!
I know. You were amazing.
We all thought so, Cyan.
Yeah? You mean it, meow?
Oops, I did it again.
--[heartbeat]
--[gasps]
[gulps]
[giggles] I always start
talking sorta weird
when I get excited or nervous.
[RETOREE]
But that's okay.
[CYAN]
Hm?
I mean, saying
"meow"-- It works.
You should use it when we talk
at our shows, and stuff.
You think so?
[heartbeats]
[RETOREE]
Uh... Uh-huh.
Retoree? Something wrong?
[heartbeats]
Oh, right!
I've got a bunch of
limited edition treats!
Do you want any of 'em?
Yeah! What have you got?
[RETOREE]
Strawberry Choco-Pies,
strawberry-flavored Pochi,
and, strawberry chips, and--
Wow! These look yummy!
Strawberries are my favorite!
[CYAN] Hey, can we watch
music videos on this, too?
[RETOREE] Oh, I have
another computer for that.
[CYAN]
You have so many!
[RETOREE]
Yup, seven of 'em, in fact.
[DAGGER]
Grateful King.
Your obstinacy has worn
my patience extremely thin.
[GRATEFUL KING]
Aw, you sweet talker, you.
[DAGGER] As I've said,
that song must be completed
very soon. Your petulant
attitude is resulting
in grave problems for
Midi City, and I'm not happy.
[GRATEFUL KING]
Yeah? What kinda problems?
Like maybe Halloween
or Christmas will end up
off-season or somethin'?
I'm sure the Myumons
who like festivals
will be real happy about that.
[DAGGER] I've about had it
with your cavalier behavior
and childish backtalk.
[OGASAWARA]
Dagger, sir.
[DAGGER]
What is it?
[OGASAWARA] Regarding
the Tsurezure incident.
Well, I just...
I couldn't get them!
[DAGGER] Didn't I say that
was your last chance?
[OGASAWARA] I'm sorry!
Next time, I will definitely--
[DAGGER sighs] Time to get
serious. I'm a man of my word.
Dear Master, how is your injury?
There is no need
for worry, I will heal.
Maybe so, but please
don't push yourself
too hard right now.
Tell me.
I have to know, who was
behind that grand apparition?
Let's just say...
Look at the world as full
of paths that all people
walk upon throughout their life.
A straight, safe path
will eventually
become dull and tedious
to those who have
walked it long enough,
and they will grow impatient.
When that inevitably happens,
they will seek out a different
path with twists and turns
to find change and excitement.
However, evil lies
in wait for them
behind every bend of that path.
And this is the reason
that monsters are now
appearing in Midi City
as of late. Do you see?
After peace continues
for hundreds of years,
something will always come to
wantonly destroy it in kind.
That is just how
the world works.
But, Master, you speak
as if you yourself
have experienced such
things personally.
[DARUDAYU chuckles]
Of course not.
It is just what I've
always been told.
[DARUDAYU]
The poor young girl.
Will she succeed,
or will she suffer?
[CYAN]
Yay, I had so much fun!
That's the most I've
ever heard Retoree say
at one time! Meow!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Hey!
[CYAN screams]
[STRAWBERRY HEART] Set break
is over. Get off your duff!
Sling your guns on
and start practicing!
Jeez, what got under
your strings?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Wake up! It's mission go-time!
What mission?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Come on, baby!
Don't you even remember
why you got rocked
into this world?
Um, I--
I have to play guitar
so I can beat down
the bad monsters, that right?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Bam!
And the only way, is to amp up
your skills to ace level.
Yeah, yeah, I know that.
But I promise I've been
working super hard
with the other girls in
the band to make it happen,
Mister Berry.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Talk is cheap, sister!
Practice first! Second!
Third, et cetera! You pickin'
up what I'm puttin' down?
Yep, that's a man
in there, but who?
Okay, if another
dark monster shows up
somewhere else, then do I have
to go fight it all by myself?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
You have an axe, use it.
That's a lot of
stuff to take on.
I'm not so sure I
can handle it all.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
That's exactly why
you gotta practice!
Yeah, but, don't you think
it seems a bit sudden?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Yup, because now
it's a do-or-die anthem.
Besides, don't you wanna burn
up the fast-track back home?
[gasps] Well, I guess
so, but I also...
[STRAWBERRY HEART] Also what?
You singin' the blues?
What? No.
I'm okay. Really,
I promise. I'm fine!
Anyway, don't worry.
I swear I'll do the mission
right. I won't let you down.
[CHUCHU gasps]
She's yappin' with her guitar?
How on earth?
That takes the cake!
[CYAN] Okay, if another
dark monster shows up
somewhere else, then do I have
to go fight it all by myself?
[STRAWBERRY HEART] Besides,
don't you wanna burn up
the fast-track back home?
[CHUCHU]
What's the skinny, here?
Whereabouts were you
living before, anyway?
Huh? Everywhere.
Kinda moved around a lot.
Are you, like, a runaway?
Let's see, Criticrista.
Wait. Listen to this--
it says they're students at
Saint Midi Girls' Academy.
S'that a big deal or something?
[gasps] You mean you've
never heard of it, honey?
I know the font's weird,
but it's "Tsurezurenaru
Ayatsuri Mugenan"!
"Tsurezure"?
[CHUCHU]
Come to think of it,
a lot of things've been
strange about her.
That does it.
I'll get it straight from
the horse's mouth! I gotta!
Our best one yet!
Yeah, we nailed it!
Perfect, pyuru!
Ha. Yep, you bet.
Oh! Chuchu, weren't
you asking me
about a new
arrangement yesterday?
Yeah, what's up?
Hey, is something wrong?
Oh, no. It's all peachy.
[CHUCHU] How am I supposed
to bring this up?
[CHUCHU gasps]
[CYAN]
Hm?
[CHUCHU] If what I think
is actually true,
how can she act like
nothin's going on?
No matter what, I have to find
out the real story from her.
Cyan. I, uh--
I know, you guys!
I have the ultimate final idea!
It's gonna completely
blow your minds!
What if we sell tons of
new merch at the concert?
It'll keep the cattle happy
and coming back for more!
Genius, right?
[YAIBA]
Merch?
Surely you're not...
I'm sorry, Chuchu.
You were saying?
It's nothing. Pay it
no mind, sweetie.
I knew the situation
was serious.
But apparently, it's even
worse than we thought it was.
[MAPLE] Mm. We need to
plan our next move.
Ah! We found it.
[CYAN]
"Shizuku Secret Mind."
[CHUCHU] It looks like
we're sharing a room.
[gasps]
[WENDY laughing]
Splash, splash!
[CORRIENTE laughing]
Ooh, it's so cold!
[CORRIENTE, WENDY laughing]
[WENDY]
Hey!
[CHUCHU]
Uh, pardon me.
[WENDY, CORRIENTE]
Uh?
Oh! Are you the
girls from Plasmagica?
My name's Corriente.
I play guitar in
Shizuku Secret Mind.
I'm Wendy, the lead singer.
Hi.
We look forward to performing
with you girls today.
[CORRIENTE] Here. Would you
like a bottle of this?
[RETOREE]
"Too Delicious Water"?
We always buy it cheap
with our employee discount
and bring some bottles
with us to shows.
Wait, what?
You have a job and you
have enough extra time
to play in a rock band?
Let me explain.
We're from Venicillin, also
called "the city of water."
So, because we've got
connections there,
we also sell mineral
water on the side
to make some extra money.
[CYAN]
Good idea!
Corriente is our
number one salesgirl.
She's killin' it!
[CORRIENTE giggles]
How cool!
[CORRIENTE]
Thanks! It's nothing, really.
Wow, it seems like you're
out on the road a lot.
Do you ladies ever
get lonely for home?
But all four of us in the band
went to music school together,
so we're like family.
We honestly don't have
much time to feel lonely.
We have so much fun,
it doesn't matter!
That sounds lovely!
It must be reassuring to have
your close friends around.
[MOA]
Hey!
Where are all the other
members of your group,
by the way?
Oh, yeah.
Shabobon and Turtle are
gonna be stuck at work
for a little while yet.
They'll rush over when
they're finished.
[MOA]
Oh, I gotcha.
On that last note, girls,
not sure if you know
yet. Check this.
There's this rumor
floating around.
[CYAN, RETOREE,
MOA, CHUCHU gasp]
What rumor?
[WENDY]
A nasty one. About band members.
Some of them have been
disappearing like magic.
[CORRIENTE] Without warning.
Presto, no more.
[CYAN, RETOREE,
MOA, CHUCHU gasp]
So what you're saying
is they're missing?
[CORRIENTE]
Bingo.
That's so scary!
[CORRIENTE]
On top of that,
you know how popular bands
are getting attacked
one after another?
Well, apparently these
incidents aren't isolated.
They're all connected
to each other.
Hey, we saw that happen,
and the one who
actually defeated--
Well, even from
the major labels,
only the popular bands
are getting targeted,
so I don't think it's
likely they'll show up
'round these parts.
I think it'd be kinda cool
if both of our bands
were popular enough
to be a target, honestly.
I know, right?
[CROWD cheering]
Okay, you cattle, let's go!
[PIG MACARON]
Crow! Ship us out!
[CROW] ♪ Shining bright
for all to see. ♪
♪ My worst disgrace,
my greatest stigma. ♪
Looks like they've
started already!
Chuchu, do you wanna
practice a little bit?
Uh, okay! That's a good idea.
[REPORTER 5A]
Breaking news.
We've just learned,
a dark monster has appeared
during the Ninjinriot concert
currently happening at S-River.
Again?
[REPORTER 5A] But the concert
was violently disrupted
and the venue is in a
current state of panic.
Updates will occur
when we know more.
Use caution.
[CYAN] Really? I still have
to go no matter what?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
No doubt!
Your mission is to take
down those dark monsters.
Yeah, but...
I'm about to go on stage!
What am I gonna tell everybody?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Who cares?
Make up some lyrics.
Just step on it!
But I... I just can't
do this. I'm scared.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Open your ears, Cyan!
I know your band means
the world to you, and I get it.
But this world is about
to go up in flames
like a nighttime pyro show.
And you're the only
one who can save it.
I know that, but... But I...
[STRAWBERRY HEART] If you know,
then light this candle!
[yelps]
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Let's go, shred it!
[CHUCHU]
Hold it right there!
[gasps] Chuchu.
Wanna tell me what's
goin' here on, missy?
Well, I uh. No. Not really.
Are you gonna go
fight the monster
that was at S-River that night?
[gasps]
What about our concert?
Were you just
plannin' to ditch us?
[CYAN whimpers]
Come on, Out with it--
What have you been hiding?
Nothing, except... I'm sorry.
[whimpers]
[STRAWBERRY HEART] Chuchu,
you gotta save it for later!
She's gotta hustle!
[gasps] Your guitar's
freakin' talking to us!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Hit the gas!
Uh...
Don't be mad, Chuchu!
I have to go right now!
Wait just a minute! Cyan!
[CYAN]
Sorry, everyone! I promise.
I'll be back before we perform!
Where's Cyan?
[gasps]
[RETOREE, MOA gasp]
[panting]
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
C'mon, speed metal!
[CROWD murmuring]
[CYAN panting]
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Did we blow it?
[MYUMON 5A]
The members of the band
got away somehow. I'm
pretty sure they're okay.
[MYUMON 5B]
That's a relief!
[sighs]
[gasps]
Hey, Mister Berry.
About the dark monster.
Do you think it could be
heading for Plasmagica now?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Huh...
I have to go back!
[panting]
[CYAN]
Please, don't let the monster
get to Plasmagica before I do!
Once I know they're
okay, I'll explain.
I'll tell them the
truth about everything.
I finally found people
that understand me.
I won't ruin that!
[CYAN panting]
It's so quiet. Maybe it
didn't come this way.
But I didn't get back in time.
The show, it's already ended.
[gasps]
You guys...
[CROW]
D'ya hear that?
I made all the cattle
knock on heaven's door
with my voice tonight!
What the--?
Hey, girl, where'd
you take off to,
leaving us all
hangin' like that?
Shut up.
Huh?
Cyan, can you finally
shed some light, please?
[CYAN]
Uh. Okay.
There's something
I haven't told you.
[breathes deeply]
Truth is, the day
I met all of you,
I'd kinda just stumbled in here
from a whole other world.
What do you mean?
[gasps]
[AION, YAIBA, ROM, CROW gasp]
You're tellin' us
you don't actually
come from this one?
Hang on. So then...
Does that mean you have
to go back sometime?
[CYAN gasps]
[CYAN]
Yeah.
[gasps]
Sorry I didn't
know how to say it
and that I hid it for
a really long time.
[whimpers]
"Sorry" doesn't make it better.
[gasps]
And by the way,
thanks for waiting
forever to tell us!
[gasps]
Retoree!
Please don't go.
[car door clicks]
[MAPLE]
Uh?
What happened here?
[CYAN sobbing]
[ROM] Will Plasmagica make
it through this mess?
[MAPLE] Mm! What doesn't
kill us makes us stronger.
There's a calm after the storm.
Life has cherries, and the pits.
All's well that ends well!
[ROM] Prez, I don't know why
you talk in bumper sticker,
but it seems to work for you.
[MAPLE] If you can read
this, you're too close!