[CYAN sighs]
[CYAN]
Hi, I'm Cyan Hijirikawa.
First year, class 3.
I'd like to join the club.
Nice to meet you.
Nailed it.
[CYAN whimpers]
[sighs]
I promised myself that
I would do this today.
But still. I'm scared.
Won't they think
I'm kind of a weirdo
for wanting to
join mid-semester?
They're already
so far ahead of me.
Dangit, why didn't
I ask to join them
right after school started?
Come on, fraidy-cat,
this is your dream,
so just go for it already!
[rock music plays]
♪ Ready! One, two, three, go! ♪
♪ Love life! Live it up!
Let's be very happy! ♪
♪ Best friends! Live it up!
Dancing, laughing! Jumping! ♪
♪ Taste this! Live it up!
Pulses racing! Okay! ♪
♪ Teenage anthem!
Come on, ready? Let's go! ♪
[CYAN]
Yeah!
[CYAN gasps]
[CYAN] ♪ Why don't we all
just live and have blast? ♪
♪ Let's fall in love at last!
Let passion flow non-stop! ♪
♪ I'm gonna dream
until the end of time. ♪
♪ Unafraid, we're flying
high and staying strong! ♪
[sighs]
[CYAN] Jeez, I need to
hurry up and turn in
my club application already!
The longer I let this go,
the harder it'll be
for me to get in, and then what?
I think they even
have training camp
during the Golden Week
holiday, too!
No matter what, I need to
join the club before then!
Oh, why do I have to be so shy?
[CYAN]
I swear I'll do it tomorrow!
[CYAN giggles] But for now, I'll
psych myself up with a game!
All right!
[gasps] Aw, yeah!
That's the highest score
I've ever gotten!
[CYAN]
Cool!
The name of this guitar
is Strawberry Heart!
That's so cute!
What the... Hey!
Shoot. Is it broken now?
[CYAN]
This is weird.
[cackling]
[yelps] Whoa. Who is that?
What the--?
[cackling]
[grunting, yelling]
[CYAN screaming]
I'm not having fun here!
[CYAN]
Huh?
Huh?!
[screams]
[CROWD]
[PIG MOUSSE]
Trichronika!
[PIG BRÛLÉE]
You're the best!
[PIG MACARON]
Shuzo!
[screaming]
[SHUZO]
♪ Don't even have to ask. ♪
♪ I know behind your mask... ♪
No!
No way!
[PIGS gasping]
[CYAN grunts]
Huh? What happened?
What do I look like this for?
[SHUZO]
♪ You and me and everyone, ♪
♪ we can be the suns that
light up the world. ♪
♪ We can give it the love
and life and warmth ♪
♪ that makes you go--
Makes everything grow! ♪
[CYAN grunting]
[CYAN]
Huh?
[SHUZO]
♪ So we will wait for you, ♪
♪ and when the day is new, ♪
♪ we will be set to burn bright
together side by side! ♪
[CYAN]
So cool...
But I've gotta be having a
crazy dream, it's too weird!
Still, who cares?
This is the most
amazing thing ever!
I wanna be playing up on that
stage like those guys, too!
[SHUZO]
Kai, Riku, we're out!
With the glittering
light of you twins,
my own major star power,
and yes, the passionate
adoration of our fans,
we'll create an
infinite rainbow.
And let it sparkle!
Yeah, right on, Shuzo!
You know it!
[CYAN gasping]
[CYAN]
Huh?
--[SHUZO] Wait,
--[thumping]
--what's that noise?
[CROWD murmuring]
[SHUZO grunts]
[SHUZO gasps]
What is this place?
Anyone know what happened?
[KAI]
I'm freakin' out!
[RIKU]
Are you all right?
[SHUZO]
Kai, Riku, be careful!
[thumping]
[SHUZO]
What's that?
[CYAN]
It just gets weirder.
If this is a dream,
I'm ready to wake up now!
[MONSTER 1A growls]
[KAI]
Uh...
[RIKU gasps]
[SHUZO]
It's coming!
[MONSTER 1A growling]
[roars]
[CYAN whimpers]
[CYAN screams]
[SHUZO, KAI, RIKU gasp]
[SHUZO]
Who's that girl?
[KAI]
Must be a fan.
How'd she manage
to get over here?
[RIKU]
Only Myumons with music skills
should have access to this area.
[SHUZO, KAI, RIKU grunt]
[MONSTER 1A growls]
[CROWD screaming]
[MAPLE] This is bad!
That's a dark monster!
President, look over there!
[MAPLE]
Criminy! Who on earth is that?
I thought we had good
security against fangirls.
She's in danger.
Emergency, pyuru!
--[SHUZO] Hello, kitty.
--[CYAN] Huh?
[SHUZO]
You don't have to be afraid.
We'll take care
of the dark monster.
The only thing you need to do
is find a safe place to hide.
[CYAN]
Uh...
[SHUZO] Come on, twins!
We've got a girl to save!
[SHUZO, KAI, RIKU grunt]
[MONSTER 1A growls]
[SHUZO, RIKU, KAI grunt]
[SHUZO] Don't let that thing
touch you with its hands!
If it catches you, it'll
drain out your energy.
Before you know it, you'll
be a dark monster, too!
[KAI, RIKU]
Copy that!
[SHUZO grunts]
[KAI, RIKU grunt]
[SHUZO, KAI, RIKU yelling]
[MONSTER 1A growls]
[SHUZO yells]
[MONSTER 1A groaning]
[MONSTER 1A roars]
[SHUZO gasps]
Kai!
[KAI grunting]
[SHUZO]
Look out!
[KAI]
Shuzo!
[SHUZO grunting]
[SHUZO screams]
[PIG MOUSSE]
No!
[PIG BRÛLÉE]
Shuzo!
[CYAN whimpers]
[KAI]
Shuzo!
[RIKU]
Easy, bro!
[KAI]
Let him go, ya bag of bones!
[RIKU]
Kai, don't!
[KAI]
Incoming!
--[RIKU, KAI yelp]
--[MONSTER 1A growls]
[KAI, RIKU yelp]
[SHUZO]
Kai, Riku!
[MONSTER 1A growls]
[SHUZO screaming]
[SHUZO grunting]
He lost the Melodisian stone!
[MAPLE]
Oh, not good.
At this rate, he'll be
turned into a dark monster
in any minute.
But he's too cute
to be a dark monster!
Those guys need help, fast.
[CYAN]
Oh, man. What should I do?
[CYAN grunts]
[CYAN gasps, yelps]
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Rock 'n roll, baby!
[CYAN]
Huh?
[CYAN gasps]
Is this the guitar
from the game?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Save it, sister!
Get in that dude's face
and play Strawberry Heart
like a true axewoman!
[CYAN]
Are you talking?!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Let the soulful rock synch up
with your Melodisian stone.
The energy will blow
that sucker away!
[CYAN]
Um.
I didn't really understand
anything you just said.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Pedal to the metal!
You gotta go save 'em!
Get the lead out, baby!
[CYAN]
Can I do that?
[KAI, RIKU, SHUZO grunting]
[SHUZO]
Kai. Riku. Hang on!
[KAI]
Shuzo. I'm sorry.
I don't think I can
last much longer.
[RIKU]
Me either.
[SHUZO]
Come on, twins, don't give up!
We've gotta fight for the fans.
It's not over till it's over!
[KAI]
It feels over.
[RIKU grunting]
--[RIKU gasps]
--[guitar playing]
[CYAN]
Their concert was amazing.
Interrupting that kind
of show is just rude!
That monster's toast!
[KAI, RIKU, SHUZO grunting]
[SHUZO]
Is that the fan girl?
Oh, wow.
Rock it, girlfriend!
[MAPLE] Well, I'll be!
That's the famous guitar.
It's Strawberry Heart!
[MONSTER 1A groans]
[KAI, RIKU grunt]
[KAI]
Our stones!
[RIKU giggles]
[SHUZO] Man, she's a
white-hot guitar goddess!
[CYAN]
Hi-ya!
[growling, roaring]
[roaring]
[CYAN]
Wow...
Uh?
[CYAN grunts]
[CYAN]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, meow!
Wait. I think I'm
back to normal-ish.
I don't know why,
but something's
different this time.
[CYAN]
Now where am I?
This is even stranger
than the last place!
[MAPLE] Excuse me. Do you
have a moment, please?
[CYAN]
Um, hello?
[MAPLE]
Ahem!
[CYAN gasps, yelps]
[MAPLE]
Hi!
Why is that egg talking?
[MAPLE growls]
Let me guess, this is just like
when you order a
hard-boiled egg.
But the yolk is runny
when you bite it?
And you say, "Waiter, this isn't
what I wanted! It's raw!"
Or like, when you're
lookin' to eat
some candy eggs, so you peel
the foil off excitedly.
And you take a big bite,
thinking you're about
to taste some delicious,
sweet chocolate.
But the inside's still
white and yellow!
Then you scream,
you lied to me!
By the way, do you
like your eggs fried,
sunny side up, or over easy?
[CHUCHU]
Enough!
President Maple.
Maybe you should get
to the point now,
what do you say, sugar?
U-Uh...
[MAPLE] Ahem! So then,
will you join my agency?
We would love to represent you.
Well, gosh. That's nice.
[MAPLE] My apologies, I meant
to introduce myself sooner.
I'm Maple Arisugawa,
the CEO of BRR.
These girls are in
a band together.
I'm Chuchu, the lead singer
and guitarist of Plasmagica!
It's nice meetin' you!
I'm the bassist, Retoree.
And I'm the drummer, Moa!
[CHUCHU]
So, cupcake, what's your name?
Um. I'm uh--
You can call me Cyan.
Cy-Cyan, meow!
--[echoing] Meow, meow, meow...
--[gasping]
[CYAN]
I stuttered on my own name!
And why did I say "meow"?
[MAPLE]
Come on, hop on the bus!
[CYAN]
You mean, with you guys?
[MAPLE]
Yes.
[horn blares]
Hey!
[CROWD screaming]
[CYAN]
Uh...
Well, hello there, kitten!
You really saved us
big time back there.
Thanks a lot!
No huge deal!
You were totally
wailing on that guitar!
Girl, you killed it!
Why don't you come with us?
Then you can sign
with our agency.
But I-- You see-- I don't...
[MAPLE]
She's gonna sign with us!
I don't care if
you're Trichronika
and signed with a major label,
there's no way you're
cutting in on my deal!
Back off, pretty boy!
--[RIKU] Shuzo, he's crazy.
--[SHUZO] 'Kay, bye!
[MAPLE]
Ow, ow, ow!
My shell! I'm caught!
Get me out of here! This hurts!
[SHUZO]
See you soon!
[CROWD screaming]
[MAPLE growling]
[MAPLE] So what if they're
popular and have fancy hair.
We've got good hair,
too-- I mean, talent.
[groans]
[MAPLE] I tell ya,
your guitar solo earlier
was massively impressive.
You've really got
the goods, kiddo!
That dark monster went
down with one chord!
Well, I was kind of having
an out-of-body
experience, y'know?
I mean, everything's
been pretty freaky
from the get-go.
[MAPLE]
Oh, don't be so humble.
[CYAN] I just followed
them without thinking.
What am I, a stray cat?
[CYAN]
Wow... Is this it?
[MAPLE]
Yep.
In the flesh,
Banded Rocking Records!
Swanky, right?
[ANGELICA]
Here you go.
I'm Angelica.
Maple's secretary and
the band manager here.
Nice to meet you.
Yes. Likewise.
[ANGELICA]
Make yourself at home.
[MAPLE] Let me get
straight to the point.
You're not affiliated with
another agency, are you?
Uh, no. But...
There are many I'd like to
join, since I love playing.
It's my dream.
It's just been kinda hard
to get my foot in the door.
Um, you know what I mean?
[MAPLE] I can't believe
a person with your
incredible talent
can't get a contract.
Oh, I wasn't talking about
getting a record contract
or anything major.
All I have to do is
turn in my application
to join a club,
but I just can't do it.
[MAPLE]
Eureka! Problem solved then!
What do you say?
Wanna be the newest
member of the BRR family?
Well, I'm thinking.
[MAPLE] True, I know we look
like small potatoes right now,
but we're about to blow up,
and I have no intention
of letting you walk out
of here without a fight.
In addition to Plasmagica here,
we've got another group
full of rowdy boys
to add variety to the mix.
I believe using these two bands
as cornerstones of
BRR will be our way
to give fantastic music to
everyone around the world.
The future will be
nothing but sunshine!
Now, come to the stage
of dreams! Please!
[ANGELICA]
President.
--[whipping]
--[yelping]
Ah!
Now, now, don't worry.
This'll be a cinch for you.
With your incredible
guitar skills,
you're unbeatable
by any standard.
Let's level up.
We all wanna sound as good as
we can, and have been thinking
about getting another guitarist.
Help make us crackerjack!
So if you're not
in another one, yet,
and you want to play,
come join our band.
[gasps] Can't believe it.
I've been wanting to hear
those exact words forever,
and I just heard them!
Joining a band...
It's my dream come true.
If you don't want to, it's cool.
No, wait. I do want to
join your band, meow!
--[echoing] Meow, meow, meow...
--[gasps]
I can't wait for it! I'd be
honored to play with you!
[MAPLE]
I'd call that closing a deal.
[CHUCHU]
Yay, this'll be so fun!
[MOA] Now there's even more
magic in Plasmagica! Pyuru!
[CYAN] But wait. I still
have so many questions.
Where in the world am I, anyway?
And also, why am I even here?
What, to do?
[CYAN]
Oh, well. I'm in!
[DAGGER]
You failed?
[OGASAWARA]
My apologies.
There were some
unforeseen circumstances.
[DAGGER] Small mistakes can
lead to giant failures.
Consider this your last chance.
[OGASAWARA]
Yes, sir!
[DAGGER] Grateful King,
have you finished the song?
[DAGGER]
Hm. I see.
Then you will not leave that
room until it is completed.
And may I remind you,
this exclusive contract
with Unicorn Virtual Music is
precisely what you asked for.
If you do not release
an album every year,
you will pay a hefty fine
for breach of contract.
Your stubbornness is
growing quite irksome.
I intend to gain control
over Sound World.
No, over the Sound Cosmos
in the very near future,
mark my words.
To do so, I need
an incomparable song
written by a
legendary guitarist,
who happens to be you.
On that note,
I've found a musician
who will be able to play
your piece perfectly.
There was some
difficulty, however,
and the player has
not yet arrived.
[DAGGER]
King, are you listening to me?
[GRATEFUL KING snoring]
[DAGGER growls]
[gasping]
[CHUCHU]
This is our studio. Cool, right?
Oh, wow. Awesome!
Wanna jam with us
a little bit, Cyan?
Jam session, pyuru!
So by jamming like,
you mean, play together?
Well yeah, what else do
you think it would mean?
Then yeah, let's go!
[CROW]
Stop right there!
[CROW, AION, YAIBA, ROM]
♪  Sing on your knees, ♪
♪ all of you cattle. ♪
♪ Be baptized in our crimson. ♪
♪ Through your reverie,
fate will be changed. ♪
♪ SHINGANCRIMSONZ,
SHINGANCRIMSONZ. ♪
[CYAN] Um, was the guys'
entrance supposed to be a joke?
[MAPLE]
Oh, no, next week, I'm sure.
[CYAN]
You're sure what?
[MAPLE] They'll play a
bigger role, maybe.
I dunno.
[CYAN]
Who are they, anyway?
[MAPLE]
I got nothin'.