[HOLMY]
All right, girls!
Battle of the bands
is this weekend.
Even though we beat Plasmagica
in the last competition,
we still can't let our
guard down, y'know?
You're totes right.
I mean, in battles, challengers
usually have a major edge
over the defending champs,
and you can't even turn your
back on them for a second
or you're gonna
get spanked, Fool!
[TSUKINO]
Mm.
Yeah, it's like the
strawberry daifuku defend,
and the melon daifuku are
launching a super-attack on 'em!
I'm starving. Let's eat!
Yup, melon daifuku
are so yummier!
Right? I know.
Hm? Hey, you knock that off!
You're being really negative!
It almost sounds like you're
expecting us to lose this thing,
and I don't want to hear it!
[JACKLYN]
Chill, Rosia!
We're only trying not to
get our hopes up too much,
just in case, okay?
[ROSIA growls]
No! Please turn that off!
Just stop it!
You're gonna make me dry
up like a wrinkly old lady!
[JACKLYN]
We can't win.
There's no chance
we'll come out on top.
They're gonna knock us out cold.
[JACKLYN gasps]
Don't do that again, Rosia.
If Jacklyn's skin dries out,
she falls into a
way major depression!
Hmph! Well, her bad attitude
was depressing me.
I get it.
But dude, Plasmagica's
hungry for real,
and they'll be looking
for revenge, girl!
The strawberry daifuku
isn't just sitting around.
It's become a stronger
strawberry cream one,
so it can defeat
the melon daifuku.
Yup, it's still delicious!
Right, totally!
I agree, too.
That's why, today...
We have to make sure
we prevent them
from winning the battle.
[GROUP gasps]
Like totally for sure!
Now don't you worry girls,
it's a done deal!
Everyone's eyes'll be
glued to my shining light!
Just like always, we can't lose!
[TSUKINO, JACKLYN]
Mm...
[HOLMY]
I-I guess you're right.
[GRATEFUL KING]
Yo!
S'up, Kingpin, you copy? Hey!
[DAGGER]
Well, well, this is a new twist.
You're actually
reaching out to me.
[GRATEFUL KING]
Yeah, I can't believe it either.
[DAGGER]
Indeed.
Then clearly you must have
arrived at wit's end.
[GRATEFUL KING]
Not really.
I just have a little of
the old writers' block.
I thought I'd talk to
someone besides myself
for a change of pace.
[DAGGER]
Writer's block, eh?
Then you've finally
decided to start putting
pen to paper again.
How delightful to hear.
[GRATEFUL KING laughs]
I'm just here to make you happy.
[DAGGER] That's cute.
Such admirable words.
You flatter me.
I thought you'd reply
with your usual sarcasm.
Would it be clearer if I used
more abusive language?
[GRATEFUL KING] Being cooped
up in such a small space
is making me tired and cranky.
It's cramping my style, man.
How about it?
Can you let me out
of this box soon?
[DAGGER]
That all depends on you.
That is, if you
understand my meaning.
I, too, am growing rather weary
of this ongoing battle of wills.
[GRATEFUL KING]
Uh...
Oh, yeah? What exactly
are you trying to say?
[DAGGER] The festival
is rapidly drawing near.
Bands who have
flocked to Midi City
in pursuit of success
and their dreams
will ferociously battle
in this esteemed arena.
I have no greater
chance than this one.
[GRATEFUL KING] So what's
the actual endgame here?
[DAGGER] Hm... I've made you
well aware of my intentions.
My primary objective is to
gather the best talent possible
for my stable.
Then, I will be the undisputed
ruler of Sound World.
[GRATEFUL KING chuckles] You'll
have to work at that a little.
You're not exactly
Mister Popularity.
[DAGGER]
Do you think I care?
Their opinions are of
absolutely no relevance.
They will quickly discover that,
and eventually have no choice
but to surrender to me.
[music plays]
It's sounding good!
Yeah, it's getting
better all the time!
Such a cool turning point! Yay!
[CYAN giggles]
[ROSIA]
Rosia from Criticrista here!
Very soon we'll be competing
in another battle of the bands!
This one will be a rematch
with the defeated Plasmagica!
They don't stand a chance.
Are you watching, Cyan?
[CYAN]
Why is she singling me out?
[gasps] Huh? Uh...
[CHUCHU mumbling]
Chuchu?
What's up?
Is something wrong?
You think maybe she's mad
at us about something?
[CHUCHU]
Yes, right. That makes sense.
I agree, we should
definitely do this.
It'll be much better.
We'll make it so.
[MOA]
Huh?
Hey, uh, you okay?
[CHUCHU] Yes, that should
do it. I think it will work.
Eureka, Cupcakes!
--[ALL] What the--?
--Pyuru?
All righty then, girls.
We've pretty much
gotten our playing down
to a perfect tee,
wouldn't cha say?
[CYAN]
Uh, sure.
[CHUCHU]
And in terms of vocals,
it's crystal clear that me and
Cyan's singin' fits like a glove
with Retoree and
Moa backin' us up!
We sound golden, and we know it!
No doubt.
Here's what's left.
--[ALL gulp]
--Okay, lay it all out.
Our performance!
--[ALL] Our performance!
--Pyuru?
Without that,
we're sittin' ducks!
[CHUCHU] But if we rock it,
their goose is cooked!
[GROUP gasp]
Chuchu... What kind
of performance?
Can you be more specific?
[CHUCHU chuckles]
You bet!
I have a pack o' brilliant
ideas to toss out!
Wanna hear 'em?
Uh, sure!
Yeah, we're all ears, Chuchu!
[MAPLE] Well, whatever direction
they seem to be headed here,
the girls are working
their tails off, aren't they?
I am as pleased as punch.
Indeed. However...
There's still a matter
of considerable urgency.
[MAPLE]
You're right, as usual.
[CYAN laughs nervously]
Shall we seek that
dignitary's counsel now?
[MAPLE]
Hmm... I suppose it's time to.
[CHUCHU]
One, two, three, go!
It's on!
[CHUCHU]
Listen up.
The winner of the battle
of the bands is chosen
not only by fans at the concert,
but also by the votes of
folks watchin' online.
[CYAN screams]
[CYAN]
Ow, meow...
[CHUCHU groans]
This isn't what I had in mind.
One, two, three, go!
--Pyurururururu...!
--[CHUCHU] Also...
winner takes all not just
by playing an awesome song,
but by charmin' the
heck out of the fans,
--the icing on the cake!
--[RETOREE] Yeah!
Go, Cyan!
'Kay!
[yells]
[CHUCHU gasps]
[thud]
[CYAN screams]
Hey, you slowpokes, if you
could finish sometime today--
[screams]
[CYAN] Spin, spin,
spin, spin, spin, spin!
[CROW screams]
Well, that's something
you don't see every day.
[ALL gasp]
[MOA groans]
[CHUCHU laughs nervously]
[CYAN] I'm spinning,
I'm spinning, I'm meow.
[CROW]
Well, you have a point.
You gotta have some flash.
Why bother doing any of
this if it's not flowery?
I understand 'cause I'm
the only one shouldering
all that showmanship
for SHINGAN, of course.
It's an Apocalypse
where I monopolize
the adoring gazes of all
the cattle. It's my job!
[AION] Silly fool. Well, it's
true that you have a garden
in your rosy, spiked head.
And it's full of nothing
but pushy little weeds
and fading flowers.
Bastard, you want me to smash
that flowery nose of yours?!
Enough.
Though it smells flowers,
the nose itself is not one.
This is simply a flowery
misunderstanding.
And hence--
Shut up! By the way,
worst analogy ever!
[YAIBA chuckles]
None of this stuff matters!
[ALL gasp]
[ROM] Please. Our fans
aren't so naïve that
they'd base a decision on
something that superficial.
[CHUCHU gasps]
You clowns. How many more
times do I have to repeat it?
This is our one purpose.
To feed the starving
hearts of the fans
with our songs and
performance, the end.
A combustion of rock and souls,
for real, no more, no less.
Am I right?
[CHUCHU gasps]
[ROM] You don't need anything
else but your real selves,
and the truth in your
music to be the best.
So go, stand proud, and win!
As I would've expected.
The man with a
full-time job brought
everyone's hearts together with
his strong, persuasive speech.
And hence--
Your words always give
me such goose bumps.
You're the best
motivational speaker.
Even this dark god
must acknowledge
the powerful light of
what you're saying.
All right, then!
So we'll kill it today, too!
'Cause we are...
[ALL]
SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
What the--?
[CROW]
They bailed!
[YAIBA]
Oh, hence.
[CYAN]
You guys? I'm sorry.
I try, but you can see I'm
really not much of an athlete.
Don't worry, Cyan.
It's not so much about
our athletic skills.
Pyuru...
Chuchu, penny for your thoughts?
"Superficial," huh?
He sure didn't mince words.
[ALL]
Mm...
[RETOREE]
Chuchu.
[CHUCHU]
Mm?
Hm?
[gasps]
[CHUCHU]
That's us.
Check it out.
We have a secret weapon.
It's right here!
[CHUCHU gasps]
Wow!
Everyone has such
a beautiful smile!
Retoree, thanks a million, Hon.
We'll perform our ultra-best
and give 'em the ultra-best
smiles on stage, too!
Can do!
Oh, yeah!
[RETOREE chuckles]
Right you are, Doll.
I daresay fun must be
our number one priority!
Master, I apologize
if I'm disturbing you,
but I've an urgent matter.
Not at all.
It's more than fine.
I was just preparing to
take a much-needed rest.
My ever-diligent disciples
could also use a break.
That's very generous of you.
I appreciate your time.
[chuckles] So tell me,
what brings you here?
The situation has
become very serious.
[gasps]
This is regarding Grateful King.
Please advise.
[music plays]
[CROWD cheering]
[MC 2A]
Now, engaging in battle today,
we have the band that
blazed in like a hot comet
and just keeps getting
hotter... Criticrista!
And the act that lost by a
hair last time, Plasmagica!
They're back with a new
song for their rematch!
[MAPLE]
All right! Look alive, girls!
[OGASAWARA]
Goo-goo-g'joo, Eggman!
[MAPLE]
Domo arigato, Mister Roboto.
[OGASAWARA]
You sure scrambled a long way
just to get beaten again.
What a terrible waste.
[MAPLE grunts] Big talk.
Who died and made you referee?
[OGASAWARA]
It's already decided!
In fact, there's no one who can
hold a glow stick to our girls,
and that scares you!
[MAPLE] Oh-ho, you
seem pretty confident.
[OGASAWARA]
It's not just confidence.
It's proof, too.
[MAPLE]
Oh, yeah, proof of what?
Rigging every contest?
[giggles]
[gasps]
[MAPLE grunts]
I'm done, let's go!
[OGASAWARA]
Huh?
[CHUCHU coughs]
We look forward to
playing with you today.
[ALL gasp]
Hey, Cyan!
--[ROSIA giggles]
--[CYAN yelps]
It's my lucky day!
I didn't know if I was
gonna get to see you again!
I... Um... Thank you?
Just so you know, I'll beat you.
[gasps]
Ha, just kidding! We're cool.
Let's just give it our
best tonight, yeah?
'Kay, we're out, guys!
[CHUCHU]
Ladies...
This ends here.
Tonight's victory belongs to us!
[ALL]
Hm!
[ROSIA chuckles]
[CYAN]
Hey, Mister Berry!
Why isn't he answering me now?
Something wrong, Cyan?
Yeah... I thought maybe he could
give me a little useful advice
before the battle tonight.
Fear not! I bet he's
gonna help you out.
There's just no way he wouldn't!
Yeah, I guess you're right!
[MC 2A]
Yo! The time has finally come
to kick off tonight's
battle of the bands!
[MC 2A]
With their major label debut
with Unicorn Virtual Music,
and their slot in the
festival already locked in.
The white-hot
superstars, Criticrista!
Hey, you guys! You're the best!
So, please. Cheer extra
hard for Cri-Cri today!
Love you, mean it!
[CROWD cheering]
[ROSIA]
Here we go!
[JACKLYN, HOLMY, TSUKINO, ROSIA]
One! Two! Three! Four!
[ROSIA] ♪ Thanks for waiting,
ladies and gents. ♪
[HOLMY, JACKLYN]
♪ It's SHOW TIME! ♪
[TSUKINO] ♪ Ready for a
cuteness overload. ♪
[ROSIA] ♪ Gonna make
your heart pitter-pat. ♪
[MOA] What was with that girl's
major attitude earlier, pyuru?
Prissy, little punk!
And how about that super
fake hug for Cyan?
[CYAN laughs nervously]
Hey, Chuchu,
you're not watching?
--Hey, Cyan!
--[CYAN yelps]
It's my lucky day!
I didn't know if I was
gonna get to see you again!
I... Um... Thank you.
We're cool. Let's just give
it our best tonight...
[CYAN]
Chuchu?
--Chuchu!
--[gasps]
Uh, yeah?
Are you okay? It's almost
time for us to play.
I'm kinda worried!
You were really spacing out!
Come on, let's focus!
Uh, right, right!
Time to get zeroed in!
[CROWD cheering]
I sure hope we did our
super cutest best today!
Everyone, you promised you'd
vote for us, you said so.
If you don't, I will never
forgive you, and I mean it!
[CROWD cheering]
[MC 2A]
Will they get their revenge?
Their entry in the festival
rides on this performance!
The challengers, from Banded
Rocking Records... Plasmagica!
[inhales, exhales]
Okay, my sugars!
Let's take 'em down!
[RETOREE]
Hm!
[MOA giggles]
[CYAN]
Mm.
With our ultra-best
performance...
[ALL]
To make the ultra-best smiles!
Ready, go! Yeah!
[CYAN] ♪ Falling through
the sky, star of dreams ♪
♪ shining brightly
in the night ♪
♪ It carries what we feel ♪
♪ Let's sing as we
all watch it fly ♪
[CYAN]
♪ Counting every star I see ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Observing quietly ♪
[CYAN] ♪ Trying hard to
hide the sadness I feel ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Have you noticed it at all? ♪
[CYAN] ♪ When I think about
what could have been ♪
[CHUCHU] ♪ My heart
starts slowly breaking ♪
[CYAN]
♪ I get so restless ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ My nights are sleepless ♪
[CYAN]
♪ I'm waiting for here for you ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ Hoping you'll
make my wish come true ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU, RETOREE, MOA]
♪ Falling through the sky ♪
♪ star of dreams, shining
brightly in the night ♪
♪ I want to be with you, then
we could watch this, you and I♪
♪ No matter how far away we
may be from each other now ♪
♪ I know someday, our two
hearts will beat as one ♪
[CROWD cheering]
[ALL gasp]
No way... No way!
[whimpers]
[GROUP gasps]
Rosia? Are you
feeling all right?
Why you trippin', girl?
[ROSIA cries]
Please, isn't it obvious?
We lost.
[GROUP gasps]
[ROSIA sniffles]
And what's worse...
...to Plasmagica.
And to that Cyan!
[CROWD cheering]
[MC 2A] Okay, Superfans!
Now it's up to you.
Which of these two
bands was more awesome?
Keep firing off those votes!
That was so much fun!
I feel like that performance
was seriously the best
we've ever done!
For sure! Me, too!
Me three, pyuru!
The results are
coming in fast now,
and that'll be our final word!
[drum rolls]
[MC 2A] What's the verdict?
Who's gonna be the champion?
[MC 2A]
I love my life. Plasmagica!
They smashed the odds,
and got their sweet revenge!
[ALL]
Yay!
Yes! We did it, girls!
We really won, pyuru!
Everyone! You're so awesome!
[RETOREE] Cyan, your
singing was fantastic!
[CYAN]
Really?
[MOA] Having you and
Chuchu as the lead vocals
was like a magic wand!
[CHUCHU]
Couldn't agree more!
[door opens]
[OGASAWARA]
Huh? No pouting.
Turn those frowns upside down.
What's the big deal?
You've already secured
your place in the festival,
so it's fine.
What does it matter if
--you lose to them once--
--[ROSIA] It's not fine!
--[GROUP gasps]
--[OGASAWARA] Huh?
You don't understand!
We're Criticrista.
We simply do not lose.
Or, I mean, we can't afford to.
[DAGGER]
She's absolutely right.
[ALL gasp]
[OGASAWARA gasps]
[stammering]
Dagger, sir! Uh...
Why are you here--
[OGASAWARA whimpering]
[DAGGER] Farewell, Ogasawara.
You're finished.
I never wish to see
your useless face again.
So, you're going to disappear.
Run, Vermin, run.
[ALL gasp, whimper]
[DAGGER]
Now, then...
You girls.
Do you possess the
slightest comprehension
of what it means to fail me?
You're wretched,
shameful, pathetic,
and a disgrace.
[DAGGER] In fact, I deeply
regret having signed you at all.
--[TSUKINO, HOLMY yelps]
--[ALL whimpering]
[DAGGER] You're worthless.
Complete trash!
--And trash gets dumped!
--[ALL scream]
[DAGGER] Goodnight, goodbye,
and good riddance!
[ALL scream]
[MAPLE]
Master Darudayu!
Does a high-ranking daruma
like you have any desires?
[DARUDAYU]
Let me see...
I would say it is for
this world to be filled
with the sound of joyful music.
[MAPLE] Your face also
resembles a lucky cat.
[DARUDAYU]
You don't say.
[MAPLE]
Hey, Miss Dayu!
[meow]