[CROW] ♪ The musical that makes
me sing the masterful quartet. ♪
These lyrics strike the
core of my crimson soul.
They're so good,
I could never get sick of them!
I'm at risk.
At risk of falling
in love with myself!
[AION]
Fatuous rodent,
it is true folly that
you are so mistaken.
Your lyrics are no more
than a tasteless side dish
to the sublime entrée
of my melodies,
there is simply no
comparison, I'm afraid.
What'd you say, punk?
Who you calling a 'side dish'?
Your songs are like the
brown scum that pools
on top of ramen!
[AION]
No, you dwarf.
Your lyrics are like the scum
and the flies that land on it!
Nobody would ever
wish to partake
of something so disgusting!
[ROM]
Shut up, all of you!
[YAIBA]
I'm not involved! Ow, my body!
I'm sick and freakin'
tired of you guys always
bickering like whiny brats!
[ALL]
Uh?
[ROM] This isn't the time to be
sword fighting for superiority.
We should only be
concentrating on improving
our new song right now,
for real. Got it?!
Wise words from the
full-time working man.
He's an inspiration to us all!
Yeah, no kidding.
You're the best, Rom,
don't ever change, okay?
Fine, I promise, I won't.
So I heard about a hot
new place to perform.
And get ready, boys 'cause
it's gonna be the next stop
on our tour of
Crimson awesomeness!
[ALL]
Uh...
[CHUCHU]
Yokai Street?
Yes. It's where
my band is based.
And it's become rather
notorious, as of late.
Oh yeah, I've read
about that place online,
but I'd be interested
to know more.
Lots of bands do
surprise shows there.
[MARIMARI]
This is true.
Many different bands
have shown up
because they read
the same things,
and they want to play
there for the exposure.
However, just as many monsters
have started appearing
at shows, too.
But more important,
didn't one of your members,
Tsugihagi, disappear
not too long ago?
[TSUGIHAGI laughs]
Marimari!
That's right, without a trace.
But where did he go?
[sobs]
If I'm clear, you've had no
luck in finding Tsugihagi,
and you'd like our
help in doing so,
is that right, hon?
[MARIMARI]
Please.
Okay, but tell me, why ask us?
When I was at the Trichronika
concert at BooDooKan,
I saw Cyan perform and thought,
"Maybe she can do something!"
Uh?! Oh, that was...
no big deal.
I would feel so much
better knowing
all of you were there, too.
Help me, girls. I'm begging you!
Kay, don't worry.
We got your back!
[gasps]
[MARIMARI]
This is where we live.
The famous Yokai Street. So,
what do you all think of it?
[GIRLS]
Wow.
[MARIMARI]
All stripes and colors of Yokai
make their home here,
hence the name.
[CYAN] I didn't know
these things existed.
[MOA]
Eesh, I didn't either!
[YOKAI CAT A]
Meow!
[MARIMARI laughs]
[YOKAI CAT A]
Meow!
The Yokai here love
to play pranks
on the rest of us, but they're
always good-natured.
So there's no need to
be afraid of them!
Kay!
[DAGGER]
Gold is nice.
It never mouths
off or defies you.
It is always obedient.
The perfect servant.
[ringing]
[DAGGER]
Hm?
Speak.
[OGASAWARA] They fell for it!
They fell for it!
[DAGGER]
Its beauty is unmatched,
and it feeds my very soul.
[ringing]
[DAGGER growls]
[OGASAWARA]
Uh. Dagger, sir.
Those patsies have
fallen for my plan.
[DAGGER] Would you care to
elaborate on that fragment?
[OGASAWARA] Oh. Yes, sir!
First, I spread rumors
about how Yokai Street
was the hottest place to be
for bands to get bigger.
Since then, they all
started showing up there.
[DAGGER]
And then?
[OGASAWARA] Mm! Sir, I did not
expect this to happen so soon,
but that girl with
the gift, Cyan,
is in Yokai Street right now.
[DAGGER]
I see.
Then off with you, quickly,
and finish the job.
[OGASAWARA]
What?! What do you mean?
[DAGGER] I mean you're
getting one more chance
to compensate for your
recent pathetic failures.
[OGASAWARA]
Uh! Thank you so very much, sir!
You won't regret it!
I'll definitely do
everything to live up
to your expectations
this time, sir!
[GRATEFUL KING]
Not gonna happen, pal.
[sighs] Won't be
much longer now.
Pretty soon we're gonna
be even more popular
than Tsurezure,
don't you think so?
We're getting
stupid rich, girl!
At the rate we're going,
I think our chances
are looking awesomely
good, for real!
[TSUKINO] Mm. I know,
it'll be easy as pie.
Duh. I always knew it'd
work out like that.
Oh, snap! There goes
Rosia's ego again!
Well, just think
about it, Jacklyn!
We are with world-famous Unicorn
Virtual Music, after all.
We're obvi super talented and
our label is like, the best.
It'd be cray-cray if
we didn't surpass
Tsurezure and Tri-chron,
and take the top spot
in a week or two.
It's good to know you're
so positive about it.
It's the truth, so
how could I not be?
[door creaks]
Am I supposed to be scared?
This looks kinda cliché, guys.
[YAIBA]
Pipe down.
I actually believe it's
pretty elegant, Crow.
So, hence--
[AION] I suppose you could
say it is sufficient
to test the skills
of a malevolent god.
But just barely.
It looks exactly like
a haunted house.
We're goin' in!
This place is major
creepy, for real.
There are literally
eyes everywhere.
[growls] You guys
quit wastin' time
and get over here right now!
[ALL whimpering]
Aion, dude. How about
you go in there first?!
[AION]
Negative.
The great sun god of darkness
is designated to go last.
Fine, then. Yaiba! You go!
[YAIBA] Uh! I will use this
golden opportunity to heed
the wisdom of the Way
of Ryu-komuso Kamui.
And take the rear guard for
all our safety. Hence--
[CROW]
Stop messing around, you jerks!
[DURADURA]
Excuse me.
[AION, CROW, YAIBA gasp]
[AION, CROW, YAIBA whimpering]
[DURADURA]
Good evening.
[AION, CROW, YAIBA whimpering]
What a bunch a sissies.
Ain't got any guts, as usual.
[AION, CROW, YAIBA scream]
What the...?
Okay.
[DURADURA] All I did was offer
them a pleasant greeting.
[AION, CROW, YAIBA panting]
[ROM]
So, what happened back there?
I have no idea...
what that... thing was.
Nor I. And my heart,
I mean, uh, the heart of
this sun god of darkness
would never tremble in the
slightest from the childish
machinations of a yokai.
Heh. Something so ridiculous
didn't even require
that I glance at my Ryukenden,
much less draw it out to
use it on anyone. Hence.
[YAIBA]
Uh. Look, there's a chair!
That's not weird at all. But I'm
sitting down. I need a rest.
[GASHIGASHI]
Gashi!
[YAIBA]
Hence!
[CROW]
Oh, man, Yaiba. What happened?!
[GASHIGASHI grunting]
[roars]
[YAIBA, ROM, AION, CROW scream]
[CROW] Things are getting
pretty interesting, guys.
Way more than they've ever been!
[ROM] Yeah, this is like
being at the spookiest
amusement park ever.
I love it! Run!
[YAIBA] Hence, this is
completely absurd, and I'm done!
[AION gagging]
[CROW]
Soldier up, Aion!
Try to pull yourself together
and get a grip like me, will ya?
[CROW groans]
Ah, great! What now?!
[whimpering]
[MONMON] Mon, mon,
mon, mon. Mon, mon!
[CROW screams]
[YAIBA, ROM, AION scream]
[OGASAWARA] Let's have
a little fun, shall we?
Tell me,
is it possible there's
some way Tsugihagi
might not be gone,
but still floatin'
around town somewhere?
Sadly, no. I wish he were.
But Tsugihagi is actually a
very shy and nervous person,
so I just can't imagine that
he would leave this town
of his own free will.
[RETOREE]
Ah...
[MARIMARI] In fact, he was
anxious about something before.
[CYAN gasps]
He told us about it.
He said he wanted to get better
at playing the keyboard
because he didn't think
he was good enough yet.
Worrying about stuff can
sure eat a person up.
We didn't really pay
too much attention
and just kinda forgot about it.
That was a big mistake!
And everyone in the
band feels terrible!
So when I see him again,
I want to make sure
he knows that.
Tsugihagi.
[sobs]
[CHUCHU]
Don't cry, sugar.
Sometimes situations
like this can be good.
They bring bands
closer together.
[MARIMARI]
Huh?
We've had several
squabbles of our own.
Right?
Oh, yeah. We had a big
fight not long ago.
[MARIMARI]
Huh?
Yup, totally! We were way
close to breaking up!
And here you are!
Congrats on clearing
that big hurdle!
Yes, ma'am.
And we're even tighter
than ever now
because we shared
the experience.
That's right!
So, I'm sure the same'll
go for your band!
[MARIMARI laughs]
Oh, I swear.
If he's hiding, and hasn't
actually been missing
from here at all, he'll
be in so much trouble.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Cyan!
[gasps] Mister Berry?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Danger's headin' this way, fast.
[ALL gasp]
Oh, no.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Yup. Monster!
Marimari, Where do you usually
have concerts around here?
[gasps] At Ushimitsu Plaza!
We have to get over there,
and it's gotta be fast!
[rock music plays]
[CROW sighs]
This is it?
"The" Ushimitsu Plaza?
At least we made
it here, dude.
If the journey to get to this
place was that hellacious,
just think. The journey back
will surely suck even more.
And hence--
Heh. Aw, who cares, Yaiba?
By the time we split,
I'll have yet another
herd of cattle mooing!
Let's go, guys.
Listen up, all you cattle!
We are wild soldiers.
And we fight fiercely
in crimson battlefields!
[CROW, YAIBA, ROM, AION]
SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
[CROWD cheers]
[TURTLE]
You da man, Yaiba!
[OGASAWARA]
You're on! Go, dark monster!
[AION]
Uh.
Hey! What the...?
[CROW]
Whoa!
[YAIBA, ROM, CROW scream]
[AION, YAIBA, ROM, CROW scream]
[AION grunts]
[YAIBA grunts]
[ROM grunts]
[CROW grunting]
[CROW] I know I'm awesome,
but can you get off me now?
[ALL grunting]
[AION] I believe we've been
removed from the concert stage.
[ROM] Did a yokai pull
this crazy stunt?
[CROW]
What?!
[ALL gasp]
[MONSTER A growls]
[CROW]
Crap. Now what?!
[MONSTER A roars]
[ROM, AION, YAIBA, CROW scream]
[ALL gasps]
[CROW groaning]
Not cool!
[MONSTER A roars]
My goodness, that's
a dark monster!
Please, no. I hope this
didn't get Tsugihagi!
Just put that nasty thought
out of your mind!
[MARIMARI whimpers]
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Let's go!
Right!
[ALL gasp]
[CYAN yelps]
I can't get in!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Great, a barrier.
[OGASAWARA laughs]
That is a shame.
Just wait, Cyan.
Once I bring these guys down,
you're next in the hot seat!
[CROW] Hey, bastard!
Wanna tone it down?
Today's an important day!
We were gonna reveal our
new song at this concert!
[ROM] I don't know what
your problem is, buddy,
but no way we're gonna
let you hose our show!
[AION]
Foolish violet yokai.
I must absolutely
forbid this nonsense.
It's blasphemy against music!
[YAIBA] You've made your
intentions clear,
now your time and
my patience are up.
It's over for you! Hence!
[CROW]
Shut your massive face-hole!
Carve the piercing
screams of our souls
into your heart, demon!
Red Tomahawk! I summon you!
[AION] Receive the holy
thunderbolt of darkness!
Behold its power!
[AION]
Holy Ark! Come forth!
[YAIBA] Time to unleash
the ancient mysteries
of the Way of Ryu-komuso Kamui.
Ryukenden, come!
[ROM]
Hit it, guys!
[CROW, AION, YAIBA yell]
[CROW grunting]
[YAIBA grunting]
[MONSTER A roars]
[CROW] Come on! Why don't
you take that ridiculous
thing off your head, barkface?!
[YAIBA yells]
[MONSTER A roars]
[AION] Go back where you belong.
Straight to hell!
[MONSTER A growls]
[AION gasps]
[AION screams]
[ROM gasps]
You guys!
Ah! Mister Berry!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Outta your hands.
It's up to the guys now!
[YAIBA groaning]
[AION grunting]
[CROW] Okay, you're pretty
strong for a yokai.
But I'm stronger, so too bad.
[MONSTER A growls]
[CROW]
Uh?!
[MONSTER A growls]
[CROW whimpers]
[CROW]
Really?!
[MONSTER A roars]
[ROM grunts]
[CROW groaning]
[CROW gasps]
[ROM grunting]
[CROW]
Rom?
[ROM] No way, man.
We're not goin' down.
We're gonna carve a burning
crimson legend of music
in Midi City, for real!
No burning stump on 'roids
is gonna ruin this concert!
[CROW]
Yeah, but--
[ROM] This is war and we're
on the front lines!
So draw your weapons and charge!
[CROW, AION, YAIBA]
Yeah!
[ROM yelling]
[MONSTER A roars]
[ROM yells]
[ROM grunts, growls]
[MONSTER A roars]
[AION]
Now, face my supreme judgment.
The wrath of the dark god!
[MONSTER A roars]
[YAIBA] Playtime is over,
giant purple people eater!
Hence...!
[CROW grunts]
[CROW]
Eat.... metal!
[MONSTER A growls]
[CROW yells]
[MONSTER A grunts]
[CROW grunts]
[AION, YAIBA ROM grunt]
[CROW] We will gaze at
this faltering world
with the crimson eyes of
our hearts. Know our name!
[CROW, AION, YAIBA, ROM]
SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
[CROWD cheers]
Wow, amazing!
They kicked that
thing to the curb!
A win for the good side!
Yeah, not too bad,
lame sauce.
[STRAWBERRY HEART laughs]
Right on, guys. You did it.
[OGASAWARA gasping]
[screaming]
--[AION, ROM grunt]
--[YAIBA] Hence!
[CROW grunts] Heh. I stole the
spotlight today, too, as usual!
They fell from the sky!
Glad to see they made it back!
[gasps]
[MARIMARI]
Tsugihagi!
[footsteps]
I was so worried.
Where have you been?
I missed you. I'm so sorry.
No, don't be.
I'm the one who owes
you an apology.
I should have listened better
to what you were saying before.
[TSUGIHAGI]
Thanks.
So it's over! He's back
now, safe and sound!
But there's something I
still don't understand.
Tsugihagi was the dark
monster the whole time?
How in the world
did that happen?
Well, uh...
I remember being sorta worried
about something, but...
It doesn't matter!
The important thing is that
you've returned to us safely!
And we have these guys
to thank for saving you!
[ALL]
Mm?
Go on, you can
give it to them.
[TSUGIHAGI]
Uh. Uh... Um. Here.
Huh? What's this, now?
Its... It's konpeito
candy to thank you.
[CROW]
Huh? What? Kon... pei... to? Uh?
[ROM]
Just take it, Crow.
[CROW]
Do I wanna eat this?
[AION gasps]
[ROM]
Hm? What's wrong, man?
[AION]
Something weird, just now.
Uh?
[gasps]
[DURADURA]
Marimari! Tsugihagi!
[ROM]
Those guys!
It's the freaky
yokai we saw before!
[MARIMARI] Oh, those are
just our other bandmates!
[AION, ROM, YAIBA, CROW gasp]
Are they any good?
[TSUGIHAGI laughs]
[MARIMARI]
Come back and visit soon!
[MOA]
Toodle-oo, pyuru!
[CROW]
Seriously?
So that huge purple tree
freak we were fighting
was a dark monster?
re you tellin' me that
you had no idea, boys?
[ROM]
Nope. None.
We assumed it was one
of the yokai attempting
to give us a good scare,
but it didn't work.
If they knew, I bet they
wouldn't've beaten it.
Ha, ha, so true!
Well, that's cool.
We just demolished a dark
monster on our own steam.
I'm so amazing!
[STRAWBERRY HEART] It's still
weird that the monster
turned out to be the
missing band member.
I know there's more to that.
[CYAN]
Yeah. It kinda makes me wonder.
Maybe the dark monsters
are just attacking
band members randomly.
This is pretty scary, you guys.
[ALL whimper]
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
That Tsugihagi kid back there.
He was worried about his
performance or somethin', right?
Yeah.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
You got darkness in your heart,
and you turn into
a dark monster.
Is that the chord progression?
[MAPLE] What? You're saying
Aion seems different?
[CROW]
Yeah.
At the ramen shop, that guy
usually gets so much garlic
in his tonkotsu, you
can't see the surface,
but he only put in three
spoonfuls last time!
Maybe he's feeling sick,
or maybe he's just crazy.
[MAPLE]
Meh. That's a normal amount.
Totally normal!
For a freak.