[CROW] ♪ Born in a moment
irresolute Crimson ♪
♪ and scarlet adorning
the crown of the head. ♪
♪ To the feet.  ♪
Crow has arrived!
[AION] ♪ Shaken by darkness
and hiding in darkness ♪
♪ and covered in darkness and
forbidden waves of black. ♪
Black monster, Aion.
[YAIBA] ♪ Searching all
throughout the land ♪
♪ to find a way to rule over ♪
♪ every savage living
thing on Earth. ♪
♪ That's the mind
of the Dragon Fox. ♪
Hence, Yaiba appears bearing
his legendary Dragon Sword!
[ROM]
♪ Secrets of men. ♪
Secrecy is what gives
grown men spice.
♪ That is the truth,
I tell you no lie. ♪
♪ For my name is Rom! ♪
[CROW, AION, YAIBA, ROM]
♪ Sing on your knees, ♪
♪ all of you cattle. ♪
♪ Be baptized in our crimson. ♪
♪ Through your reverie,
fate will be changed. ♪
♪ SHINGANCRIMSONZ,
SHINGANCRIMSONZ. ♪
[CYAN whimpers]
Tch. Dangit, Aion!
You came in early and cut
me off before I was done!
What's your deal?
I've no problem, you
foolish and weak rodent.
In front of me, the
Dark Sun God himself,
your angry cries mean little
more than dust in the wind.
Shut up, Wimp-ion!
And do you have to pose
every single time you talk?
You screwed up, too!
You went on way too long, Yaiba!
It always sounds like you're
about to forget the lyrics!
It makes me nervous!
Doing so is the very essence
of the Way of Ryuko
muso Kamui. Remember?
Hence, we make it a point
to shorten your time,
since you are short in stature.
[CROW]
Oh, is that so?
Then it would seem the
two of you are itching
to get your souls erased.
Red Tomahawk! Come!
[AION]
You are foolish to defy a god.
Take your best shot!
[AION]
Holy Ark! I summon you!
[YAIBA] Hey! You cretins aren't
leaving me outta this!
Ryukenden, come!
[yells]
[YAIBA, AION yelling]
[ROM]
Shut up!
[CROW groans]
[YAIBA, AION groan]
What is this, a playground?
You guys do nothing
but fight all day long!
[ALL gasp]
[ROM]
We are crimson souls, remember?
We've gathered at the foot
of destiny called a "band,"
each sharing the same
fate: to carve out
a legend into music history.
Or have you forgotten?
Wise words from the
full-time working man.
He's such an inspiration!
No kidding. You're
the best, Rom.
Don't ever change.
You've even managed
to convince a god.
Well done.
All right!
Let's show the world
what we're made of!
We are...
[ROM, YAIBA, CROW, AION]
...SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
[gasping]
In case you were wonderin',
they're the other band
that's part of this agency.
To be clear, SHINGANCRIMSONZ
and Plasmagica are the
entire talent roster.
[laughs nervously]
What's with all the
jibber-jabber over here?
Who let cattle into
the sacred place
where we polish our souls?
"Cattle"?
Mind your manners!
She ain't cattle!
Her name's Cyan.
She's our newest member!
She's not some random
SHINGANCRIMSONZ groupie!
Not that "groupie" is all
that flattering either,
but you should really stop
calling your fans "cattle."
[CROW]
What did you say?
It cannot be helped, though.
Crow's parents are both
common dairy farmers.
Hence, he--
Shut your talk-hole!
A lotta good that milk did me!
I drank it daily and
never got any taller!
Dairy farmers? Whoa.
You talkin' smack about
what my parents do?
Uh--!
Back off, okay?
Cyan hasn't gotten used
to being around y'all yet.
Leave her be till she learns
how to tolerate you.
"Tolerate us"?
More like "tolerate our
skyrocketing success"!
We will carefully polish
our burning souls,
[CROW, AION. YAIBA, ROM]
and stand tall
at the top of Midi City one
day! For we are SHINGAN--!
Woa! It's just like
I thought it'd be!
Now that Cyan's joined and
added her talent to the mix,
Plasmagica can begin
the second chapter
of our legendary spot
in music history!
[gasps] Really?
[MOA]
Well, obviously, pyuru!
You don't have to
hold back, you know.
Feel free to try whatever.
Oh...
Okay, I wasn't sure
what I was allowed to do,
'cause, uh, I've never
played with other people.
But I had so much fun doing it!
I'm glad you asked me
to be a part of your band
--and everythi--
--[stomach growls]
[gasps]
[CHUCHU] Uh, let's stop there
for the day, sound good?
[CHUCHU]
There's a café down
on the first floor
of this building.
We always eat dinner there
after rehearsal's over.
[MOA]
Gotta replenish our energy!
[MAPLE]
Money, money, money!
Though it's useful, there are
some things in this world
money can't buy.
Once again, you're
drinking too much.
--Moderation is the key.
--[MAPLE] Lay off!
We're in the business
of selling dreams here!
Of touching people's souls!
Our job is to make good
music, not money, got it?
Make good music, not money.
What are you drinking,
loud juice? Jeez.
[bells jingle]
Hey, there! Welcome.
Evenin'!
Our agency president runs
this place as a side business.
[CROW growls]
[CYAN gasps]
These guys again!
[ANGELICA]
Here you go! Bon appétit!
It's delicious!
[CHUCHU]
I know, right?
Hey, get a load of this crap!
We get really
thirsty making music.
That's why we drink
Dream Galactica Cider!
Uh--
We're the Dream Galaxy Idols...
...known as Trichronika!
Everyone out there should
be drinking this, too!
Then we can search the
dream galaxy together!
[grunting]
[AION]
Ridiculous.
That "dream galaxy idol"
stuff is complete nonsense
to a god like me.
Yeah, you said it!
Even so, we don't really have
a proper catchphrase
like that, do we?
In preparation for the
television commercial
that will surely
come calling one day,
why don't we consider
what will be our
Legend of Catchphrase.
Like for example:
"When pursuing the
cries of savage dragons
born of the ancient
flames of purgatory."
"Hence, we--!"
You're talking about
your Ryukenden, right?
You're so predictable.
[AION] How about:
"Spun from the dark evil,
but holy psalms."
[CROW] Black Monster, right?
You're just as bad as he is!
Ah! I don't know
why I brought it up
to you nitwits in
the first place.
Hey, Rom! You got
any ideas, man?
I'm busy organizing
receipts right now.
Don't talk to me.
Oh. The receipt thing?
Rom works for some company.
[CYAN]
He has a full-time job?
[MOA]
Yep! He wears two hats!
Wow.
Come on, Rom!
Blow that off for now.
Let's think of something
cool that'll blow
Shuzo's lame saying
right out of the wa--!
[ROM]
Shut up!
[groans]
Don't say that moron's
name around me!
What's your problem, Rom?
How many times do I have to
tell you never to touch my face?
Keep your trap shut!
Geez, Rom.
Your Legend of Violence
appears to be
even worse than usual.
This is ridiculous!
Who cares about catchphrases?
Who cares about dream
galaxy idol? It's all crap!
Isn't our way of
living our catchphrase?
Ever think about that?
[groans] Oh, Rom. I'm sorry
I ever doubted you.
You're the absolute best.
[phone ringing]
[MAPLE]
Hello? Yes, speaking.
Yes. Uh-huh. Yes. Yeah.
[MAPLE]
Yes! Yes! A million times yes!
Good news, SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
I found work for you
fine young gentlemen!
[CROW] Really? Awesome!
What kind of work?
[AION] Depending on what
this "work" may be,
the god may not
deign to descend.
True.
We shouldn't agree without
careful consideration.
Hence--
[CROW groans]
Come on! Don't leave
us hangin' here!
Tell us about the job, Prez!
[MAPLE] You'll be the
opening act for Trichronika
at tomorrow's concert
in Shibu Valley!
Isn't that wonderful?
Uh--
We're going to be
their opening act?
[MAPLE]
I was told the band
that was supposed
to go on all came down
with some kind of tummy-bug.
Too bad for them, but that means
that the job of pinch hitter
has suddenly fallen
into your laps!
Ha! I'm not interested
in being the opening act
for a bunch of
idol nimrods. Later.
[ANGELICA]
Oh, Rom!
Work is work.
You have to take everything one
step at a time in these matters.
Don't you agree?
All right! Fine! Whatever!
We'll do it! Are you happy?
Yes. Good boy.
[MAPLE]
Now that that's settled,
let's make sure we go all out!
Show those boys a thing or two!
[CROW laughs]
Well...
Look how excited he is!
Overboard if you ask me.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
[MAPLE]
Oh! By the way, Cyan.
I was wondering...
Where exactly do you live?
Where I live? Well, uh...
[MAPLE grunts]
All the rest of us
live in the dorm
in this lovely building.
It's totally fun!
If you wanted, you could
move in here too, Cyan!
Sound good?
That's a great idea!
Wow! You mean it?
Yes, I'd love to,
if it's no trouble.
[CYAN sighs]
Yes! I'm saved.
Whereabouts were you
living before, anyway?
Huh? Everywhere.
Kinda moved around a lot.
Are you, like, a runaway?
No, it's nothing like that.
[CHUCHU] She doesn't seem
to wanna talk about it.
We shouldn't pry. It's
probably sad and complicated.
[MOA] Maybe she can't
reveal her true identity.
Could she be like me?
[RETOREE]
Dat awkward face, though.
[CHUCHU] Okay, Cyan.
This'll be your room.
You should mention
something to the president
about getting more
furniture in here for you.
Oh! Yeah, sure!
[RETOREE]
Here you go.
[CYAN]
Uh...?
They're pajamas.
Thought you'd need some.
[gasps] I appreciate it!
Goodnight, then!
See ya in the mornin'!
[MOA]
Sleep well, pyuru!
Yeah. 'Kay.
Pleasant dreams!
[CYAN] I have to do this.
I have to say it properly.
I, uh--!
[CHUCHU, MOA, RETOREE]
Hm?
Uh--! I just... wanted... to...
...say good night, everyone!
Night-night!
[sighs]
[CYAN]
Aw, man.
It shouldn't be this hard
to thank them for inviting me
to join their band.
It's all so crazy.
Why'd things turn out like this?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Are ya homesick already?
[gasps] The guitar talked again!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Sorry about leaving you alone
like that. You must've
felt all shook up, honey.
Yeah, you could say that.
I've felt alone plenty
of times in my life.
But it's different here.
I mean, I don't even know
where I am or anything
about this crazy place, so...
[STRAWBERRY HEART] This is
one of the 12 city-states
in Sound World, and
it's called, Midi City.
Midi City?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
A chaotic and cool music city.
This is where Myumons,
musical beings like us, live.
Everything in this place
revolves around music,
and all Myumons love music.
[CYAN]
Oh, really?
Um, I was also wondering why
I have these things on me.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Because you've become a Myumon!
Huh?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Don't worry.
It's just your temporary
form while in this world.
When it's time for Myumons
to perform, they can
transform into bodies
designed for that
specific purpose.
[CYAN gasps]
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Dig it: the stone that shines
in your chest? That is what is
known as a Melodisian stone.
It contains the sound energy
hidden within all living beings
in this world.
With excellent music,
it resonates with the
audience and becomes
a crystal of high fidelity.
However, if it comes in contact
with dark music energy,
it becomes tainted
with dark Melodisian.
It's just so strange,
it all happened so fast.
And while I'm beyond happy
to be asked to play
in a band that's as
amazing as Plasmagica...
I don't know.
I don't understand why
I'm in this place at all!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
This world is on the brink
of a tremendous crisis,
and you're the player
that's been chosen to save it.
I was chosen to save the world?
Are you serious?
There's just no way. I can't
do something like that!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Unfortunately,
until you're able to polish
your musical abilities
and annihilate the dark monsters
who bring forth the dark music,
you cannot return
to your own world.
Wha--? No way!
I can't. It's impossible.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
You did a pretty killer job
of driving the
enemy away before.
That was just dumb luck.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Your performance saved the day!
They're alive, thanks to you.
How 'bout it? You ready to rock?
Yes! I'll rock!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Really? You'll take on the job?
Um, if possible,
I'd like to join a club
before the Golden Week holiday,
so it'd be great if I could
go home by that time.
But, until then, I'll
try to save the world.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Ahem.
[CYAN humming]
♪ Why don't we all just ♪
♪ live and have blast?
Let's fall in love at last! ♪
♪ Let passion flow non-stop! ♪
♪ We're running,
aiming for our future. ♪
♪ Everyone together.
A happy ending! ♪
Huh?
[CYAN] ♪ But what will
tomorrow bring for us? ♪
♪ Is happiness a bust? ♪
♪ Let's work to make it last.
I'm gonna dream until ♪
♪ the end of time. ♪
♪ Unafraid, we're flying high
and staying strong! ♪
[sighs] Baths are just
the greatest things ever,
am I right? Meow?
[STRAWBERRY HEART
laughs nervously]
[CYAN]
Huh?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Uh, hey, did you write that song
you were just humming?
[CYAN]
Yeah, maybe, why?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Try playin' it for me.
Wha--?
But it's so late, I was
about to go to sleep.
[knocking]
Uh, yes? Come in, please!
Mind if I bug you
for just a minute?
[CHUCHU] Believe it or not,
this here is the first song
I ever wrote.
Wow! It's really good!
Thanks! And this
is the second one.
Oh, it's super cute!
And the lyrics are
really moving, too!
You think so? Hey,
so I was wondering.
Do you write songs?
Uh-- Yeah, I guess. Kinda.
Was what you sang
earlier one of them?
[CYAN]
What? Oh. You heard that, huh?
[CHUCHU] The bath echoes.
I'm sure everyone heard it.
Ah...
[knocking]
Come in.
I brought clothes.
Thought you'd need some.
[gasps]
[MOA] I had a feeling
everyone would be in here!
I brought some yummy snacks!
The president is the one
who brought us all together.
He scouted the entire group.
[gasps] Really? That's so cool!
One day, we want
Plasmagica to perform
a solo-headlining concert
at the BooDooKan.
That's our goal until we're
able to do bigger and better.
As for me,
I guess you could say
I'm a fan of music.
But, then, I'm kind
of awkward, so...
[RETOREE]
I can't say it!
Under no circumstances
will I admit
that I joined a band
to make friends!
I love music, too!
It makes my insides happy!
[MOA]
Pyuru-ru-ru-ru, ru-ru-ru-ru-ru.
Cyan, I'm really
glad you joined us.
We're looking forward to
making great music with you!
[RETOREE, MOA]
Totally!
[CHUCHU] I can't wait until
we get to perform together!
Yeah! Same here! It's gonna
be a blast, for sure!
That's it, then.
I'll work hard and
practice playing guitar
each and every day so I
can defeat those monsters.
After all,
joining Plasmagica is
like a dream come true!
Nothing could make me happier.
I think I can work
hard for a while
just because I wanna
be great for them.
Huh? He must be asleep.
[FAN 2A]
Shuzo!
[FAN 2B]
Trichronika!
Our boys didn't say
a word to each other
on the ride over, did they?
Those guys put the
lame in lame-sauce.
I'm worried about their show.
Come on, get it together!
What're you doing gettin'
nervous now? It's pathetic!
[knocking]
[STAFF 2A] SHINGANCRIMSUNZ!
You're up! Let's go!
Okay, Rom! Say
something! Pump us up!
All right! Let's rock!
Show 'em what we're made of!
[MC 2A]
Good evening!
Welcome, everyone, to tonight's
Trichronika concert!
[CROWD cheers]
[MC 2A]
I know you're lookin' forward
to seein' those boys
as soon as possible.
But first, give a warm welcome
to our special guests:
SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
[PIG MACARON]
Huh? What the crap?
I'm only here for Shuzo!
[PIGS]
Boo! Boo!
[CROW] With our crimson gaze,
we keep watching you
and loving you. We are...
[YAIBA, CROW, AION, ROM]
...SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
[CROW] All right,
you cattle! Let's rock!
[PIG MACARON]
Did he call us... cattle?
Who're you calling cattle?
Are you trying to
pick a fight with me?
[CHUCHU groans]
Oh, rats, he said it.
He's totally the
worst, you know?
Is he really that stupid?
Everyone here is a Trichron
fan. They're not his cattle.
[gasping]
[CROW] ♪ Shining bright for
all to see my worst disgrace, ♪
♪ my greatest stigma. ♪
♪ Misery, it rains upon me,
blinding me with suffering. ♪
♪ Oh! My heart's been
mutilated and abused. ♪
♪ And yet, it flows
with crimson, ♪
♪ still wandering all alone. ♪
♪ Falling Rose. Falling Rose. ♪
♪ Save me from
this pain untold. ♪
♪ Give me the warmth... ♪
[PIGS cheering]
[CYAN] Wow, they managed
to win everyone over!
[CYAN] What these bands
can do is amazing!
Music is like magic here!
[CROWD cheers]
Now it's our turn, guys!
Ready to put on a good show?
[KAI, RIKU]
You bet, Shuzo! Let's go!
[laughs] Didja see that?
Those cattle are
ready to be shipped!
Hey, SHINGAN!
Thanks so much for
being our opening act!
We appreciate you!
What did you say?
After that glorious crescendo,
you think you can just--
Hey, Rom! Take it easy!
Don't do anything stupid!
[SHUZO]
Hm?
We warmed up the
crowd for ya, buddy.
[AION]
That we did.
Hence.
Kai, Riku, let's go!
[KAI, RIKU]
Sure thing!
[CROWD shouting]
[MAPLE]
Oh, goodness me!
That was wonderful work, boys!
I believe I was the
popular one today.
[AION] Bantam dwarf, the stares
aimed in your direction
were little more than
dust compared to those
lauded at me, the black monster.
[YAIBA] There was no
greater applause tonight
than that which was for
my Ryukenden Dragon Sword.
[CYAN]
Hey, everyone!
Uh.
I wanted to say, when you
asked me to join the band,
I, uh, it made me
really happy. So, uh...
Thank you all so very much!
[ROSIA]
Hmmm.
So that's Plasmagica?
[MAPLE] That band is
making its appearance
in the next episode!
[CHUCHU] Huh? What do
you mean, "that band"?
[MAPLE]
An MG band!
You know, Middle
school Girls! Yay!
[CHUCHU] President, you're
a little too excited
about this and it's creepy.
[MAPLE laughing]
[CHUCHU]
Ugh.