[AION]
"An ant killing an elephant"
is an apropos phrase
for this scenario.
To think that a god-like black
monster such as I would be
worried about the insect-like
pebble that entered his shoe.
[AION] Additionally, a chunk
of this long, unruly hair
is pointing up at the sky as if
it is somehow being summoned
back home from above.
[AION]
This is the worst.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Dark monsters have been known
to take advantage of
darkness in people's hearts.
The darkness in their hearts?
And what does that mean?
[STRAWBERRY HEART] Oh, you know,
like in Yokai Street.
Little Tsugihagi turned
into a monster, remember?
If you put the pieces
together, it all makes sense.
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Listen to me, little sister.
That Dagger gives me
a dirty, dirty feelin!
I see.
Then I guess we need to
be extra careful too, huh?
Also, you've started talking
even more strangely than usual.
Awesome, y'all!
Seems like all that's left to do
is practice this song even more
and then it'll be
completely ours.
[ALL giggle]
Hey, what do you
think, Mister Berry?
Again?
Is he sleeping?
I don't think so.
For a while now, it seem like
his spirit leaves sometimes.
But lately, it's been
happening more and more,
and I don't know why.
Goodness, how strange.
Well, whatever the case,
we're actually playing
the Grateful Rock Festival.
It's unbelievable,
like a dream come true.
But... what happens if we
don't leave a good impression?
[MAPLE]
Oh, no! Terrible news!
Well, about that "terrible
news" you mentioned?
[MAPLE]
Uh!
Unfortunately, from
what I've gathered,
it looks like Plasmagica
won't be able to perform
at the festival!
[ALL gasp]
We can't? Why not?
[MAPLE]
I filled out the application,
just like you're
supposed to,
and included a demo of the
song you'll be performing,
"Falling Star Dreamline."
Thankfully, the song
passed muster.
But then, there's this.
This!
What's that all about?
A "Live Point"?
We have to have played
a live show before?
Well, that sucks. We haven't
done a proper concert as of yet.
So, does that mean
we can't perform?
Wait, what about Shingan?
Are they ineligible, too?
[MAPLE]
Nope.
Remember when they
opened for Trichronika?
Even though it wasn't
a headlining show,
it still counts.
So, they passed
with flying colors.
[ROM] It's not something
we're proud of, though.
[ALL gasp]
Yo, Plasmagica,
how long are you gonna
drag out your rehearsal?
My Red Tomahawk is
anxious to come out,
plug in, and totally
rock your world!
Sorry 'bout that.
You can't be in that much of a
hurry. You're not all here yet.
What?
Uh.
It's true.
I thought he'd be
meeting us here,
but I don't see Aion anywhere.
You didn't notice
until just now?
Wonder what excuse he'll have
for not being here on time.
He'll prob'ly be like,
"The sun god of darkness has
low blood pressure right now."
Or some stupid crap like that!
If he spouts out a lame excuse
like what a nine-to-fiver
would say, like "traffic,"
he's gonna regret it!
Anyway, back to us
and the festival.
We've come this far. We can't be
disqualified on a technicality.
Let's do whatever it takes
to make this happen.
[MAPLE] I have an idea
or two about just that.
I'll tell you more
about it at the café.
[MAPLE] You should
play in an even bigger
and concert-worthy
battle of the bands!
Are you serious? Another one?
Wait a sec.
You don't mean a rematch
with Criticrista, do you?
[MAPLE] I knew you'd be the
first to catch my drift, Chuchu.
What? But Cri-Cri is
on a roll right now!
They're super popular!
It would be so embarrassing
to lose to them again.
But right now, it's not an
issue of winning or losing.
We just need to play
a high-profile show
to count as a concert.
With that new song of ours,
I think we actually
stand a chance
of beating them this time.
[ALL gasp]
If we win this, and bring
that momentum to the festival,
then... we'd definitely
be the number one band
to watch out for.
Well, that might be true,
but it's not something
to get worked up about.
Right, yeah, I suppose not.
But would they
even be up for it?
Will they accept our challenge?
[MAPLE] That's where the might
of your powerful president
comes in!
I'll call Ogasawara. Uh...
Right now. Yep. Any second.
I can't do it! Oh, the pressure!
[ANGELICA] Hello? This is
Banded Rocking Records.
Yes.
I was calling to ask for a
battle of the bands rematch
with our artist Plasmagica.
Yes.
I see. Excellent to hear.
We look forward to
working with you again.
It's all set. We're ready to go.
She's awesome.
[MAPLE]
And how.
[ANGELICA]
However,
their appearance and performance
schedule is pretty booked,
so it has to go
down next weekend.
Next weekend?
That doesn't give
us a lot of time.
Look, it's been decided,
okay. We need to practice.
Let's do it.
But wait, we can't.
Right now Shingan
is using the studio.
[CHUCHU]
Uh.
Oh yeah, I forgot.
Hey. Let's call it a day, 'kay?
Sounds good to me. We're
playing great, so why not?
[ROSIA]
Mh-hm.
And that means, snack time.
Girl, I dream about snack
time all night long.
So what yummies are
we having today?
Cream puffs with extra cream.
[ALL giggling]
[TSUKINO]
Bon appetite!
Wait.
[BOTH gasp]
[DAGGER]
Hello, ladies of Criticrista.
[ROSIA]
Mister Dagger.
[DAGGER]
Plasmagica just called.
They'd like to have another
battle of the bands with you.
[ALL]
Uh?
[DAGGER] I accepted, of
course. But will you do it?
Yes. It's just what we wanted.
[DAGGER]
Is that so? Excellent.
[JACKLYN] Rosia forgot
to keep her cuteness up.
[TSUKINO]
I wonder what's wrong with her.
She's way serious about it.
This time, we'll
beat them so bad,
they'll have to crawl away
on their hands and knees!
[DAGGER]
Love the attitude.
But don't forget, the
enemy is quite powerful.
Is your bite as
vicious as your bark.
[door opens]
[OGASAWARA]
Hey!
Plasmagica wants to
challenge you girls again.
We already know!
[OGASAWARA]
Oh!
Sorry.
Ah! I'm tired of waiting!
The flow of time is limited
and cannot be changed
at the whim of one's discretion.
If humans are weak beings
subject to the
fragility of time,
then we have no choice
but to treasure each
second of life we have.
Hence, we should...
Whatever, let's just
start without him.
Fine, then play already.
[door opens]
[ALL]
Hm?
Where have you been?
We've been sitting
around here forever!
You're so late the strings
on my precious Red Tomahawk
were about to rust and fall off!
Enough! Wouldja hurry up
and get ready to play?
For you to be this late,
you must've been involved in
some kind of Legend of Accident.
Hence--
[CROW] Hey, Aion,
are you even listening?
Whatever. Just grab your
axe and get ready to rock.
Oh, yeah.
About that new song of yours
you brought in the other day.
we're having a hard
time nailing it
'cause the order's
all over the place.
Think of the rest of us who
have to perform this stuff.
[sighs]
We can't always depend on
my amazing lyrics and vocals
to save every little
lame, weak-sauce song
that creaks outta that
head of yours, so-- Uh?
What's with that bit of hair?
[CROW chuckles]
What is going on
with your dome, bro?
[CROW laughing]
"Lame, weak-sauce songs," huh?
Maybe you're right. Maybe I've
been kidding myself all along.
Don't be stupid.
Whoa, Aion, you're not posing.
[AION]
I hate anything and everything.
I quit.
[MOA]
Wha?
I knew it! There's no
practicing going on in here!
If that's the case,
would y'all mind if we used
the studio to rehearse?
Did something happen?
[ROM]
Ugh.
This is all your fault!
It's because you called Aion's
songs "lame, weak-sauce."
And then you laughed
at his bed-head?
What are you, a little
kid or something?
Huh? So this is all my fault?
You heard what I said!
[BOTH growling]
No. This isn't the first time
Crow took a jab at Aion's music.
Hence, it-- Uh.
[CHUCHU]
Let me get this straight, Yaiba.
The perpetually gloomy Aion was
1.6 times gloomier than usual?
That just barely made sense.
Hey, remember what happened to
Tsugihahi from Shinimonogurui?
Mister Berry said that
sometimes dark monsters come
and latch onto the gloom
in Myumon's hearts
so they can influence
their minds and bodies.
You mean that--?
Maybe the same thing
happened to Aion.
If that's the case, shouldn't
you be out looking for him?
Yeah, guess you're right.
I concur, as well. Hence, we--
[CROW]
I'm not going!
[BOTH]
Uh?
Oh, come on, Crow!
Aren't you worried in the least
about what's happening to Aion?
[CROW] Nope. Saying
"I quit" is taboo, man.
That bastard. He said it like
it was no big deal at all.
Who cares? He can
go do what he wants.
All right, then.
We'll just go out and
look for him without you.
I think everyone should
help track him down.
Yeah.
We can cover a lot
more ground that way.
Pyuru.
Thanks. That's nice of you.
He could come back here, Crow.
And if he does, he
might not be himself.
Find a way to keep
him in the studio.
Whatever. Like I care.
We'll be back in a bit.
[grunts]
[ROM]
A place where Aion would go?
[CYAN] Yeah, like to think
or be alone. Any ideas?
[ROM] Well, stores related to
music seem the most likely.
[CYAN]
Okay, where else?
[ROM]
For now, that's it.
Let's just look everywhere we
can come up that he might be.
[RIKU] Wow, that was
a great concert, Shuzo.
[chuckles]
Well, thanks a lot, but I really
owe it to the two of you.
You twins really worked
hard to make me shine.
You really think so?
That's so nice of you to say.
[gasps]
Shuzo. That guy over
there looks familiar.
Isn't he a member of the band
that opened for
us the other day?
SHINGANCRIMSONZ?
[KAI] Why is he up
there on the roof top?
[RIKU] Whoa. He's putting
off a really negative aura.
[ROM] He may be a shut-in
with a communication disorder.
He can't talk to anyone
unless he poses.
But no one in the band would
argue that he's the most
musically talented and the
biggest fan of music among us.
That's why hearing him say
he was quitting the band
was something I never
thought would happen.
[YAIBA]
Hence...
[ROM]
Yeah, and that Crow.
He's always dogging on Aion
and saying mean things,
but he's the one who
recognizes his talent the most.
The songs filled with
soul that Aion writes
combined with the passionate
lyrics that Crow adds to them,
are refined by us,
and then become new
SHEENGANCRIMSONZ music.
So to lose Aion...
Is just unthinkable!
Rom.
I don't wanna watch a
friend leave like that.
Never again, you understand?
[horn blares]
[YAIBA]
This is... Trichronika's limo.
[growls]
Ah, hey, Rom.
Hence, I--
We meet again.
What do you want now, Shu?
We're kinda busy here, okay?
Ah, the lovely nostalgia.
You're the only one who
calls me that these days.
[YAIBA]
Hm?
[ROM]
Tsk.
So, anyway,
if you happen to be
looking for a guitarist
being eaten away by
a squirming dark aura,
I just happen to
know where he is.
You what?
That's none of your business!
We don't need your help--
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but isn't he your
precious band mate?
Ha. Unless you wish misfortune
to befall yet another one
of your dear friends.
[gasps]
Damn you, Shu.
You might try the Shibu
Valley Center Building.
[ROM]
Uh.
Buh-bye now!
Rom.
Yeah, right, let's go.
[SHUZO] What's with the
doom and gloom, you two?
Got something on your
mind that's bothering you?
Well, uh...
You see.
We were wondering
about that drummer Rom
you were talking to earlier.
Did you know him before the gig?
I mean it seemed like you
were old friends or something.
[SHUZO] Once, there were
band mates who shared a dream.
The goal of one of these friends
was to make that dream of
theirs a reality someday.
He valued that above
everything else.
Truth be told, however,
the other friend also wished
to receive blessings
from that dream.
Even though the dreams they
chased were one in the same,
in time, they found they could
not walk together anymore.
They broke their chains and
went their separate ways.
I'll tie him up and drag
him back if I have to.
That was my intention
from the start.
Hey, Aion!
[ROM]
Idiot!
What're you doing
in a place like this?
[AION] The god has already
announced his departure
from SHINGANCRIMSONZ.
What I do up here all by myself
is none of your concern.
Aion!
You bastard!
Don't spout anymore
of that nonsense
about you quitting
and leaving us!
[AION]
Someone like me.
[ROM]
Huh?
Even if... I wasn't
there, you'd--
Are you still saying that crap?
Rom!
Enough, you idiot!
[ROM yells]
[ROM]
Crow.
[CROW] Sorry, but I can't
allow you to leave us.
It's not gonna happen.
And even more than that, I can't
allow you to make this guy sad.
[CROW] He was crying
'cause you left him.
Now listen up, Aion!
You haven't quit SHINGANCRIMSONZ
yet, understand me?
None of us has officially
accepted your resignation!
So there!
And, well, maybe... I might've
mouthed off too much, too.
But don't say annoying and
stupid things like "I quit"!
I'll only say this once,
so pay attention!
[CROW]
I will never allow a band member
who wrote such beautiful and
soulful songs to leave us!
We need that muse
more than oxygen!
Can't you see
they're our lifeblood?
We can live our
lives passionately
because of your music!
This god made the
mistake of a lifetime.
I can't believe
it took the wisdom
of this under-sized
rodent to save my soul.
Oh, shut your talk-hole.
[AION]
Uh.
My eyes. Are these tears?
I thought they had
dried up long ago.
Through rain, fire,
flood, whatever.
When the four of
us are together,
there's nothing the world can
throw at us we can't overcome.
Even if a monstrous
wall blocks our way,
when we work as a team, we'll
find a way to bust through it!
[CROW]
Damn straight! Because we are...
[ALL]
SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
What's that? You found him?
Oh, thank goodness!
[ROSIA] Well hello,
fanboys and fangirls!
Rosia from Criticrista here
with a totes important
announcement for you.
Very, very soon,
we'll be competing in another
battle of the bands.
This one will be a rematch
with the defeated Plasmagica.
They don't stand a chance.
Are you watching, Cyan?
[gasps]
This time around, I'll
flatten you like a pancake.
Just kidding!
[giggles]
We'll see you then!
Don't forget to vote, 'kay?
[SHIBARIN]
It's finally time
for the Grateful Rock
Festival, y'all.
[POKOE] There's gonna be a whole
buncha popular bands there.
[HAKKUN] I wanna go to Midi
City. I wanna see 'em play.
[SHIBARIN] You gotta
fight to get some tickets!
[POKOE] We could check
out some online auctions.
[SHIBARIN] They're really
expensive, though.
High schoolers like us don't
stand a chance of winnin'.
[POKOE]
Didja hear about Cri-Cri?
They're doin' another
battle of the bands.
[SHIBARIN] What band are they
dukin' it out with this time?
[POKOE] Plas-- Uh.
Plasmagica? Or something?
[SHIBARIN]
Who the heck is that?
[KITTSUN] Sorry! That dang
math class is the pits!
Huh? What's wrong guys?
[POKOE, HAKKUN]
We wanna go to Midi City!
[KITTSUN]
Oh! Midi City's great! Let's go!
We should make gettin' some
new trendy clothes there
our first priority.
[POKOE, HAKKUN]
Huh? Clothes come first?
[SHIBARIN]
Who's this Plasma-thingamajig?
[KITTSUN]
Wait, what are we gonna do
about the school festival?
[HAKKUN] Come on, don't
drag me back to reality!
[SHIBARIN] I said, who's
this Plasma-deeleebopper?
[MAPLE] Today, we have
Rosia from Cri-Cri.
Let's cut to the chase.
What's your favorite hobby?
[ROSIA]
Shopping, doi.
Like, trying on cute clothes,
looking at myself in the mirror,
and then the clerk says,
"That looks so fetch."
It's the best thing
ever. I love it.
[MAPLE]
OMG, me too!
What'd I just say?