[CYAN]
Here it comes!
Pyuru!
Got it!
And spike!
[whimpers, groans]
Cyan!
--Everything's spinning...
--[CYAN] We're at a beach
outside of Midi City right now,
and so far, we're
having a lot of fun.
Are you all right,
cupcake? That smarts!
I'm so sorry!
[CYAN] President Maple
sent us to a training camp
to write a new song to perform
at the Grateful Rock Festival.
You okay now?
[CYAN]
But before we got to this point,
we went through a
pretty major nightmare.
I, uh...
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Oh, Mama! Someone start singin'!
'Kay. Wait. I think--
Did that guitar
just... say "Mama"?
You think that's strange?
[STRAWBERRY HEART] Ahem.
This kid's completely shocked,
so I'm gonna give
you the feedback.
You all first met Cyan during
the Trichronika concert--
You remember that
night, rock stars?
We were able to beat
that dark monster down
with her mad guitar skills,
and of course, my muscle.
Now, I'm sure that
image is probably
still branded in your minds.
As long as this girl's playin'
power chords, we can
make the dark monsters
ancient history.
Then, can we
assume it was you
who brought her to
Sound World, rock candy?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
No, she was yanked here
against her will
by someone else.
The president of Unicorn
Virtual Music, Dagger Morse!
[CROW, AION, YAIBA, ROM,
CHUCHU, MOA] Dagger Morse?
So, by "Dagger," you mean
the bigwig who controls
the entire music world?
[CROW] On top of that,
that dude is the sole owner
of the ultimate
major record label.
And they represent one of
the only guitarists I respect,
Grateful King!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
You done, chief?
The reason he dragged
Cyan all the way down here
wasn't to fight dark monsters.
Because Dagger's actually
the one controllin' those
giant purple freaks!
He's after mad skrilla, man!
He's plannin' to
take over Sound World
and make it his own evil empire!
He wants the most talented
musicians at his agency,
and to 86 any other rival bands.
The dark monsters are
his weapons of choice.
In order to make a grab
for this world, Dagger had
to troll other ones.
That's where he found Cyan,
and zeroed right in on her.
[CHUCHU] So this is
all Dagger's dirty work?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
He brought her here by force
to be part of the "perfect band"
he's putting together.
But I made sure to get right
in his way because, man,
do we need her.
[MAPLE]
And that's where I rolled in!
At the perfect time,
I might add!
So you're tellin' me
that you already
knew the truth about Cyan
when you convinced her
to join Plasmagica?
[MAPLE]
Yes. So, please.
It's not all Cyan's fault, here.
I'm not such a good egg.
We're very sorry, Chuchu.
[MAPLE] You see, I wanted Cyan
to level up her music skills
with you all. That way,
you could evolve
your Melodisians together.
And then, you could beat Dagger
at his own game and
knock the shady snake
out of commission!
Why did you hide that?
It isn't fair.
I know we all would
have understood you!
[MAPLE]
I didn't wanna burden everyone
with something so heavy
right from the get-go.
You girls are like
daughters to me!
That's how you think
of us, President?
It wasn't because
you conveniently
forgot to mention it?
[MAPLE]
E-hoo...
[MAPLE groans]
Quit dragging your
little feet, Egg Man!
This Dagger bastard's
sittin' pretty in that tower!
You should go
straight over there
and give him a sharp
piece of your shell!
All right, boys!
Let's raise us some hell!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Stop, look, and listen now!
That's my philosophy.
Only fools rush in, Daddy.
[ROM]
U-Uh, sorry?
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Uh-- Save the brute force.
Money's his version of
the same thing, ya dig?
You wanna beat that guy?
Music is the key to
strikin' him down.
[AION]
We must...
...defeat him...
...with music!
Yeah, baby. I'm gettin'
super fired up!
[AION, YAIBA, ROM yell]
[CHUCHU] Can it, boys.
That's not the issue right now!
[CROW, AION, YAIBA, ROM]
Huh?
No matter what the case,
you can't skedaddle
before a show like that!
[gasps]
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Well, that one's on me.
But, y'know, Cyan was
puttin' the music first,
just like the rest of you
rockers. I made her leave.
[CYAN]
That's not it.
I'm the one who chickened
out and said nothing.
I'm the one who took off
before the concert.
This is all my fault.
I'm so, so sorry, Chuchu, Moa.
Every show is important, I know.
Aw, it's all good.
[CYAN] I need to apologize
to Retoree, too.
[CYAN] Listen. I really
need you to know this.
You see...
The truth is, Plasmagica means
more to me than anything.
Oh, we know it does, pyuru!
Isn't that right, Chuchu?
[gasps]
[MAPLE]
Okay! It's settled!
[AION, ROM, CROW, YAIBA]
Huh?
[MAPLE] Our agency will
have a training camp!
[YAIBA, ROM, CROW, AION, MOA,
ANGELICA] Training camp?
[MAPLE]
Yup, you heard me!
Eating your meals together.
Sleeping in the same room.
Having no-bull,
on-the-level conversations.
And getting rid of
all your hard feelings
by sharing some good,
old-fashioned leisure time.
Except that we're not
going there for fun!
[CROW]
The Grateful Rock Festival?
That event is 100% legendary!
[MAPLE]
Yep, it's pretty popular.
[CROW]
Oh, legend! Ah, ha, ha, ha!
[MAPLE] I'd like for you
all to write new songs
to play at this festival.
Get packed up.
We're leaving tomorrow!
[CROW]
♪ Legend! ♪
Well, where's this
training camp we're off to?
[MAPLE] Where every good
training camp should be!
In the mountains of course!
[CHUCHU, MOA, CYAN,
RETOREE scream]
[CROW, AION, YAIBA, ROM]
Wait, it's up there--?
[CHUCHU]
Hey.
Angelica, can you tell
us where we're going?
I think you're gonna like it.
Oh, wow.
It's all sparkly!
[CYAN grunts]
[CYAN sighs]
[CROW, YAIBA, ROM coughing]
[MAPLE] Come on, you guys!
Put your backs into it!
This is part of your
training, too, by the way.
[CROW]
Damn it.
We'll use up all of our
strength before we even
get to training camp!
If this wears you out,
then you're a
freaking cream puff.
[YAIBA]
I'm with Rom on this one.
You know, the more you complain,
the weaker you will
start to become! Hence!
Push, you big crybaby!
Hey, you push, too, Wimpion!
[AION] A divine, evil god
is whispering in my ear,
"You must refrain from strain."
[growling]
[sighs]
I can't do this anymore.
I gotta take a break.
[ROM] You're missin' the big
picture here, dummy.
[CROW]
Huh?
If we push as hard as we can,
our bodies and minds are
only gonna get stronger.
And that means our
performance at the festival
will be awesome, too!
This is our chance to be
the best, so don't piss it away!
Oh, crap. Rom, you're
totally right, man!
The only guitarist I respect,
the legendary Grateful King
once said something
I'll always remember.
"When you're in trouble,
most of the time,
you're being tested!"
I will go right to the
Legend of the Other Side!
It's about teamwork!
If we pool our strength,
we can do anything!
[ALL yelling]
[AION]
I'll pick up your bones.
[ALL screaming]
[MAPLE]
Can we get a move on?
[yelling]
[CROW, YAIBA, ROM yelling]
[MAPLE]
Oh, pah!
[CROW, ROM, YAIBA]
Ah.
Ah, ha, ha...
[MOA]
Pyuru. Just look at this place!
[door squeaks]
[ALL]
Hm?
[HOTEL MANAGER 6A speaks]
[CYAN, CHUCHU, RETOREE, MOA]
Uh...
[MOA]
President? That you?
It's one of his relatives.
They look totally alike!
I'll be in the room
right next door, ladies,
so you just give me a shout
if you need anything.
[HOTEL MANAGER 6A speaks]
Anyone want some tea?
There's a fruit plate, too.
No, that's okay. I think
I'll save room for dinner.
I'm gonna go to the hot tub.
[door clicks]
Uh, yeah, me, too.
Yay, then so will I!
On second thought, I'd
rather sit back down again!
[CYAN] Thanks, you guys.
I appreciate it.
Wish me luck.
[RETOREE]
Hang on.
So then, does that mean you
have to go back sometime?
[CYAN gasps]
[CYAN]
Yeah.
[gasps]
The thought of her
leaving makes me wish
she'd never come here.
[sighs]
[CYAN]
Retoree?
[gasps]
[CYAN]
Um.
Oh, boy, here goes nothing.
I'm gonna come clean
with you now.
I mean, this is a hot tub.
So I'll bare all since
we're naked in here anyway!
Ha, ha, just kidding.
[CYAN] I'm so sorry,
but I didn't have the guts
to tell you till now.
The thing is,
I've loved playing guitar
ever since I was little.
I wrote all my own songs,
and played them by myself,
'cause I was alone.
[CYAN] At first, I had
enough fun just playing
and singing without
anyone else around,
and so I got used to it.
[CROWD cheering]
[CYAN] Then, when I watched
the high schoolers
play music, It made me wanna
be in a group someday, too.
But I was way too shy
to ask to join the band.
When I found myself here,
and I got to join Plasmagica,
that was the best day ever.
Hey, Retoree, ya know what?
I really wish that...
that I'd told you this sooner.
Don't get me wrong,
the girls are great,
but I feel even worse
because you matter to me
more than anyone.
[whimpers]
[CYAN gasps]
[door scrapes]
Do you think Retoree's
still mad at you?
Y'know, I don't think that's it.
She seems more sad than mad.
The reality is,
she's upset because
you'll be going back
to your own world soon.
You said "your own
world," didn't you?
Even when that
happens, you and I
will still be right here,
so we have to make
a serious effort to
get closer to Retoree,
so she's not unhappy.
Pyuru... ru... ru.
Dang it, Rom!
You lied when you said
"we're almost there,"
Yeah, right!
Have we not completely
lost the pathway
we should be following?
And, hence--
[AION]
We're stuck in an infinite hell
where we won't even reach
the oracle, aren't we?
What do you want from me?
--And how about you guys--
--[rustling]
[CROW screams]
Prez, is that you?
[HUNTER 6A] Why're you
filthy animals running wild
in my hunting grounds?
My hair! No! No! No!
[ROM] I realize this may
be an inopportune time.
But I'd like to give
you my business card.
[HUNTER 6A]
Whaddaya want?
You don't have to
be suspicious of us.
The truth is, we've been
separated from our party,
and we're trying to
locate and rejoin it.
[AION] Well, Rom is the only
one of us with a real job.
[HUNTER 06A]
City boys, huh?
Welcome to the jungle.
Come with me.
What d'ya think?
Grateful King also said this:
"When you meet a
hunter in the woods,
most of the time, he's a
pretty decent fella."
[AION] Gentlemen, can we really
trust this man's character?
Or Grateful King's jokes?
[HUNTER 06A] Y'all are
terrible hungry, ain'tcha?
[AION, CROW, YAIBA, ROM]
Ah, ha...
[ALL laughing]
[CYAN]
♪ Counting every star I see, ♪
♪ observing quietly, ♪
♪ trying hard to hide
the sadness I feel. ♪
♪ Have you noticed it at all? ♪
♪ When I think about
what could have been, ♪
♪ my heart starts
slowly breaking. ♪
[gasps]
[CYAN]
♪ I get so restless. ♪
♪ My nights are sleepless.
I'm waiting here for you. ♪
♪ Hoping you'll make
my wish come true. ♪
♪ Falling through the sky,
star of dreams, ♪
♪ shining brightly
in the night ♪
♪ I wanna be with you. ♪
♪ And we could watch,
just you and I. ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU, RETOREE] ♪ No
matter how far away we may be ♪
♪ from each other now,
I know someday, ♪
♪ our two hearts
will beat as one. ♪
[RETOREE] Hey, Cyan, you said
something a while back.
That when you're
with your band mates,
you can speak more clearly
with music than with words.
You're right. It's true.
[gasps]
I understand that.
And I can accept it.
I mean, I do!
Retoree! Thank you, meow!
[gasps]
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Y'all checkin' outta
the Heartbreak Hotel?
[RETOREE]
Uh, you're floating.
[CYAN]
Why are you making fun of us?
This is serious, y'know.
Quit joking around!
[STRAWBERRY HEART]
Aw, don't be cruel
to a Strawberry Heart
that's true!
Now, everybody, let's rock!
Thank you. Thank you very much.
[CYAN growls]
[CHUCHU]
Hey, guys.
[RETOREE, STRAWBERRY HEART,
CYAN] Huh?
Where'd Moa go?
[MOA]
What should I do, pyuru?
It's too late to tell
'em the truth now!
[CHUCHU]
Don't be crazy, Moa!
[MOA]
Oh, no.
Why are you over there?
Because there's something
that I've kept hidden
from everybody, too!
[RETOREE, CHUCHU, CYAN gasp]
I, Moa, am about to send
an important transmission!
All right, sweetie.
We're here listening to you!
Very well then. The whole
truth about me is...
I'm an alien
from another planet!
I was sent to
investigate this one!
And I started with you!
[CHUCHU, CYAN, RETOREE]
Huh?
[RETOREE]
Wait, hold up.
There're only four
people in this band.
Isn't it kind of lame and
gimmicky for two of the members
to be aliens from
different worlds?
[CHUCHU]
I think it's Moa's sweet attempt
at making Cyan feel better.
[CYAN]
Thanks, Moa!
It's okay, you don't
have to do that anymore!
I swear I'm not lying!
[CHUCHU]
Hold your horses! Lightbulb!
Can we use this?
It would totally work!
We could have a whole
outer space theme!
Oh!
Then you and I have
to think of an idea
for a gimmick, too, Chuchu!
I can't believe this.
They think it's just
an act. Well, watch this!
Pyurururu-rururu!
[RETOREE, CHUCHU, CYAN gasp]
[RETOREE, CHUCHU, CYAN scream]
[RETOREE, CHUCHU, CYAN]
Moa!
--[rumbling]
--[RETOREE, CHUCHU, CYAN yelp]
[RETOREE, CHUCHU,
CYAN whimpering]
[MOA]
I'm sorry.
I couldn't tell you all, either.
Retoree, please,
don't be mad at Cyan,
'cause I did the same thing.
[RETOREE]
I'm not mad at anybody now!
Huh?
[RETOREE]
Listen to me, Moa.
All four of us are
in this band together,
that's the only thing
that really matters.
I don't care what
planet you come from.
Right now you're here with us,
making music, so let's enjoy
ourselves while we can!
I couldn't have
said it better, hon.
[MOA gasps] Wow, thank you!
You girls are the best!
[RETOREE, CHUCHU, CYAN yelp]
[MOA groans]
[RETOREE, CHUCHU, CYAN]
Moa!
[MOA]
Sorry, pyuru.
[CHUCHU] We certainly made
fine use of our first day here.
[CYAN]
Mm-hm.
[CHUCHU]
Here's an idea!
How's 'bout we polish
the song we just sang?
We can make it the new
one for the festival!
[gasps] Do you mean it?
And just so you know, angel.
I'm choosing you to
be singin' the vocals
right there with me on this one.
[gasps] Are you sure?
Ever since I first
heard the sugary sound
of your beautiful voice,
I decided we'd make
a terrific team.
I dunno. I'm not great
singing to a crowd.
I think you'll rock it.
[gasps]
Yeah, I do, too, pyuru!
I love you guys!
Now, since we'll be playin'
at the Grateful Rock Festival,
I want Plasmagica
to leave an impression that
no one will ever forget.
You feel me?
[RETOREE, MOA, CYAN]
Yeah!
[CYAN]
And so, that's pretty much
how we kicked off training camp.
[HUNTER 6A]
All right den. Be good.
[ROM] Thanks. We owe you
one, old man. For real.
[HUNTER 6A, ROM]
It's the real rock!
[CROW]
Grateful King!
I'm gonna write the
greatest song ever,
the same way you did!
'Cause you're my hero!
Hence, what the hell are
we doing this for, man?
[AION]
I don't know!
Now that's more like it.
[YAIBA] In Midi City,
there are numerous places
where not even I have
stepped foot. Hence--
[MAPLE] Hence-- You should
go to Yokai Street.
It's a devilish mystery!
[AION] A mysterious devil
from the world of spirits?
Is it finally time for this
sun of darkness to take action?
[MAPLE]
Carpe diem, baby!