[SHIBARIN sighs]
The school festival's over.
[POKOE]
That was fast.
[HAKKUN] But I still
wanna go to Midi City.
[door rattles]
[KITTSUN] Sorry! That dang
Spanish class is the pits!
Huh? Que onda, gueros?
[ALL grumble]
[KITTSUN]
Stop, one at a time!
[SHIBARIN]
Playin' fer two and a half hours
with just three songs
takes a lot outta ya.
[KITTSUN] Actually, we
spent most of our concert
doing more talking than playing.
Whew, I'm beat too!
[SHIBARIN]
I'm plumb wiped out, y'all.
[POKOE]
It'll be six more months
'for somethin' intrestin'
to yap about.
[KITTSUN]
Gotcha.
Listen, there's
something important
I forgot to tell everyone.
[ALL]
What is it?
[KITTSUN] When we performed
at the school festival,
this weird guy Ogasawara
gave me some tickets.
And check it out, they're for
the Grateful Rock Festival!
[ALL gasp]
We're goin' to Midi City?!
[ROM]
What?!
Dagger's scheming to
plant these things
at the Grateful Rock Festival?
[MAPLE]
Yes, I'm afraid that's right.
[CROW] Leave it to me.
You've seen by now.
I can take down those clowns
with just my bare hands.
Crow, man, you've gotta
knock that stuff off already.
Yeah, yeah. I know.
To beat the dark monsters,
no, that dirty, rotten Dagger.
we have to use the
power of music, right?
[ROM gasps]
Yes. Ryukenden will ensure it.
That base Legend of a Villain
will never be allowed to darken
the doors of the BooDooKan.
So, hence--
[AION]
The song played by the Holy Ark
of this dark sun god will become
an equally holy thunderbolt
that will convict
and punish Dagger,
the very incarnation
of evil most foul.
Hah! Looks like we're
all on the same page.
No matter what happens, we won't
let that legendary festival
be defiled by his corruption!
[CYAN]
Mister Berry.
He hasn't talked to me at
all since we saved Chuchu.
I don't know.
What's happened to him?
[MAPLE]
Hm...
[CYAN gasps]
Come on, Rock Candy!
Usually, you won't
shut up! Start talkin'!
Crow! You leave him alone!
Whatever.
Gracious. This mess
is totally my fault.
I'm so sorry.
No way. Not even
close to your fault.
[CHUCHU]
Cyan...
It was Dagger, he tried
to brainwash you.
He's the one we
should be mad at!
Yeah, the creep!
[CHUCHU]
That's very sweet of you to say.
[DAGGER]
Utter genius!
King, the songs you write
are truly second to none!
[DAGGER] Compelling,
deep, and overflowing
with ecstatic energy.
One could search
everywhere in Midi City,
and find nothing
remotely comparable.
You may be King, but
I'm going to be Emperor!
Phenomenal work.
Nobody does it better.
--[DAGGER laughs]
--[GRATEFUL KING panting]
[GRATEFUL KING] You used a
petty trick like brainwashing
an innocent girl.
What, regular manipulation
wasn't enough?
Is this as slimy as
you get, or is it worse?
[DAGGER]
Slimy? No need to flatter me.
Besides, I'll win.
That's what matters,
"slimy" or not.
[GRATEFUL KING]
Hah!
Your clichéd plot failed,
though, didn't it?
You're nothing but a cheap thug.
[DAGGER] No plotting.
I was just playing around.
Having some fun.
You're the one exhausted
and ill from participating,
which amuses me.
Now that I have this song,
I already consider my
goal accomplished.
You know, you're
gonna get burned
if you underestimate her, right?
[DAGGER]
Hmph. All things considered,
she doesn't stand a chance
against this music's power.
Anyway, I kept up my
end of the bargain.
So c'mon! Keep yours
and let me out, man!
[GRATEFUL KING]
Hey! Bastard! What's wrong?
Do you have
selective hearing now?
You really are a shyster!
I hope your tentacles fall off!
[coughs]
[DAGGER]
Aw... Not feeling well?
I suppose naïvely falling
for a verbal handshake
would make me rather sick, too.
[GRATEFUL KING grunts]
[DAGGER] You might as well
give up, get comfortable,
and watch what unfolds
at the festival
while you're
trapped like a rat.
I guarantee, it will be
the best entertainment
since the inception
of Midi City. Enjoy.
[laughs]
[gasps]
[DAGGER laughing]
Don't do this, man! Dagger!
Prepare yourself, Cyan.
[GRATEFUL KING]
Kiddo... You've gotta win this.
Dear Master,
since our performance
in the Grateful Rock Festival
has been appointed for us,
I have been dutifully taking
care of my precious guitar
shamisen and also refining
my technique to perfection.
I've been rehearsing my bass
shamisen and my singing.
I'm certain, too, that I've
improved quite significantly.
I greatly admire
your dedication.
Skilled musicianship
is a vital virtue.
However, my dears,
have you forgotten what is most
paramount at the present time?
[BOTH gasp]
We are so honored
by your kindness,
but what more can be
done in this situation?
After learning of
Dagger's nefarious plans,
I will also put my fate on
the line to help destroy him.
You don't comprehend!
[BOTH gasp]
Our primary objective
is to share the music
of the Far East with people,
that they may know its beauty.
It is crucial, that
we perform our music
from the very depths
of our hearts.
Authenticity is the only key.
No matter what catastrophe
looms before us,
if we remember that key,
we can and will eliminate
any such threat handily.
I profoundly regret having
misunderstood you.
I must apologize as well.
All is forgiven.
In the long run, it doesn't
change your unwavering
devotion to me or my teachings.
Use that as encouragement,
so you may continue to
stand firm with me here.
Now then, shall we retire
for luncheon at last?
[BOTH]
Yes!
[DARUDAYU] Dagger, I will
not allow you to jeopardize
Midi City, the music,
or the people!
[SHUZO]
Kai, Riku, getting close.
Are you guys about ready
for the festival, too?
Yup! We're ready
for anything, yo!
The only thing we have to do now
is fill the hearts of
the fans with pleasure,
excitement, sparkles,
and shine like the sun!
Let me tell you something, guys.
We have the most wonderful
job in the world.
I'm even envious of myself!
Yup. We couldn't agree more.
It's on!
[SHUZO chuckles]
[CROWD cheering]
[CHUCHU]
BooDooKan...
We have arrived, oh yeah!
I know!
It's almost showtime, pyuru!
Can't believe it. We're
actually gonna perform here!
[CROW laughs]
Holy crap, guys!
This is awesome, this is
awesome, this is awesome!
Yeah, I'm getting way
fired up, for real!
[AION] This is surely
the holy land of music.
It's the Biggest Legend
of the Concert Hall.
--And hence--
--[CROWD cheers]
[gasps]
[A, UN panting]
Look, you guys! It's Darudayu!
Well, hello again.
Let's give our all tonight.
To fill our hearts and those of
our loving fans to the fullest.
Yes, Master, pyuru!
[DARUDAYU]
By the way, Cyan.
Uh, yeah?
No matter what may befall
us here this evening,
you must firmly believe
in your own immense power.
Huh?
--[car honks]
--[gasps]
Hey!
[CROWD squeals]
Here they come.
It's Trichon's Rangers.
[ROM grunts]
[PIG MOUSSE]
Shuzo!
[PIG BRÛLÉE]
Kai!
[PIG MACARON]
Riku!
We're here!
You can start now!
We're gonna put on a brilliantly
shiny concert for you!
Y'know, like we always do!
Hang on.
My, my, if it isn't the
brave little kitten!
Uh. Yeah, I guess.
Thank you for that.
Oh, no.
We're the ones who owe you a
major debt of gratitude, girl.
Wait a sec.
You're Plasmagica, am I right?
Heck yeah, they are!
You guys are the hottest
band in Midi City right now.
We are? That's so nice,
thanks again!
Let's make this concert
sparkle together, 'kay?
[SHUZO]
Hm?
[SHUZO] Show me what
you're made of, Rom.
If you can handle it.
[ROM] Wipe that smug
look off your face, Shu.
'Cause we'll win. For real.
[CYAN] Mister Berry,
it's finally time.
[CHUCHU]
Hold everything.
The President and Miss Angelica
still haven't arrived
yet, have they?
[RETOREE]
They said they had some business
to take care of first,
and that they'd rush
right over afterwards.
What kind of business?
[MAPLE]
Angelica, step on it!
[ANGELICA]
All right, president.
Fasten your seatbelt.
It'll be a bumpy night.
[MAPLE screaming]
[CROWD cheering]
[MC 2A]
The long wait is over, everyone!
Comin' atcha live from the
world-famous BooDooKan arena.
It's kickoff time for the
Grateful Rock festival,
generously organized by
Midi City's hometown hero,
Grateful King!
So, ladies and gentlemen.
Buckle up, and
start your engines!
[CORRIENTE] Hi, girls!
Why don't you have some?
Oh, thank you so much!
Super cool to see you again!
And there's a lot more
where that came from.
Warning!
You can only have two
bottles for free, though!
How slick, no wonder
you're number one in sales.
[CORRIENTE gasps]
It's a living.
Anyway, ladies, we'll
liven things up, won't we?
[CYAN, RETOREE]
Yeah!
'Course!
We're all about it, pyuru!
Knock, knock, we're coming in!
It's Marimari! And Tsugihagi!
[TSUGIHAGI]
Uh, I brought some snacks.
Help yourself.
You're so thoughtful!
Well...
It has been quite a while
since we've seen each other!
I can't wait!
Tonight is a longtime
dream come true.
And we all get to
share the same stage!
Yeah. It's great, isn't it?
[CYAN] Everyone's so psyched
about the festival,
but I have a bad feeling.
[CROWD cheering]
[MC 2A]
Leading the pack!
The band who holds
the number one spot
in Midi City, Trichronika!
[CROWD screams]
[SHUZO] ♪ Don't even
have to ask, I know... ♪
[CROW] Jeez, about time
we've been asked to play
this mind-blowing festival.
I mean, it's like the world
finally figured it out,
and has just now caught up
to the greatness that is me.
[AION]
Be that as it may.
Grateful King, the one you
worship second only to
this dark hallowed sun god,
is apparently missing
from the long list of
concert participants.
It would seem that means
he may not descend
upon this place today.
Nobody worships Aion as
much as he worships himself.
Still, I'll keep quiet.
You mean you guys didn't know?
I heard a rumor, see.
Grateful King has been
holed up in a great studio
to focus greatly on a
new song. Correction.
I mean he's there to focus
on writing a great new song.
So hence, he won't be making
any manner of appearance
at the concert?
Nah...
Although, he could still
be a total rock star
and surprise us all.
That'd mean, maybe we
could both jam together!
Because really, the only one
who could keep up with King
is the great and powerful Crow.
[squeals]
Wouldn't you agree, man?
[CROW]
Hello...?
[ROM gasps]
You okay there, dude?
Uh, yeah. I'm fine.
Just prepping to go on.
Now, let's do this thing!
[CROWD cheers]
[MC 2A] Next up, it's the
band lighting up Midi City
like a raging bonfire with
their crimson mind's eyes.
SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
Hey, you cattle,
you about ready?
[PIG MACARON]
I love it when you talk dairy!
This is so weird.
I just realized
Criticrista isn't here yet.
Good. They'd be throwing
mad shade at us already.
So true.
I can't believe they'd be
late for a show like this!
[CHUCHU] And I definitely don't
think they would just skip out.
[CHUCHU]
Keep your chin up.
[CYAN]
Huh?
Don't you worry, Cyan.
We're here.
All of us are gonna
support you, 'kay?
Pyuru! So you're not alone!
Yeah. Thanks, you guys!
I mean it.
[CROWD cheers]
[MC 2A]
They came to grace Midi City
with the haunting, beautiful
sound of the Far East.
And took everyone's hearts
hostage in an instant!
The lovely and exotic
Tsurezurenaru Ayatsuri Mugenan!
[DARUDAYU] ♪ See the blooming
of wonderful fireworks above ♪
♪ Hear the train blow
its whistle in the night ♪
[A] ♪ Oh my heart, it
beats so uneasily ♪
♪ In the dryness of
a sleepless night ♪
♪ Apprehension
hangs in the air ♪
♪ So I respond with
one step forward ♪
Mercy! What's that racket?
Don't tell me.
[CROWD murmuring]
[DARUDAYU gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[DARUDAYU]
And so it begins.
--[UN yelps]
--[BOTH grunt]
[DARUDAYU] Girls, brace
yourselves, immediately.
[A]
Master!
[UN]
There you are!
[DARUDAYU] Dagger has
finally made his nasty,
long-awaited move.
[gasps]
[KAI, RIKU, SHUZO grunt]
[SHUZO]
What's happening?
[YAIBA, AION, ROM grunt]
[CROW groans]
[RETOREE]
Oh, not again.
[MOA] Please, don't tell me it's
another dark monster, pyuru!
[CHUCHU gasps]
Cyan!
[CYAN]
Huh? Where are we?
[gasps] Darudayu!
[DARUDAYU] Ah. Excellent.
This is a reassuring sight.
However, our enemy tonight is
a criminal the likes of which
we've never dealt with before.
You must not let
your guard down!
--[MONSTER 11A roaring]
--[ALL gasp]
[ALL gasp]
[RIKU]
Shuzo, look!
[CROW]
Where is it?
[UN, A]
Master!
[DARUDAYU]
There you are.
[MONSTER 11B roars]
[UN, A yelp]
[CHUCHU, CYAN, MOA, RETOREE]
Ahh!
[MONSTER 11B roars]
[AION, YAIBA, ROM gunt]
[CROW]
Ugly bug, isn't it?
[SHUZO]
Kai, Riku! Stay behind me!
[MOA whimpering]
[DARUDAYU]
This is my cue.
[MONSTER 11B roars]
[DARUDAYU yells]
[ALL gasp, grunt]
[scream]
[CROW yells]
[SHUZO]
Jump, now!
[KAI, RIKU scream]
[SHUZO]
Kai! Riku!
--[RETOREE, CHUCHU scream]
--[MOA] Help, pyuru!
[UN, A yelp]
[CYAN whimpering]
[gasps]
[CYAN gasps]
You guys!
[ALL whimpering, grunting]
[CROW]
Crap, I can't move.
[CYAN]
Everyone! What should I do?
[SHUZO] Hello, Kitty!
Work with me, won't you?
Together we can defeat it!
I believe in you!
[DARUDAYU] That is a task you
must leave to me, I'm afraid.
[CYAN]
Darudayu!
[DARUDAYU] You two
should save your strength
for the titanic battle
that will ensue.
You're definitely
going to need it.
[CYAN]
But I have to--
[DARUDAYU] Do not
worry yourself, Cyan.
I am more than
equipped to dispatch
a creature of such
magnitude on my own.
[DAGGER]
All my obstacles are eliminated.
Dark monster, seize those
pests, and do it now!
[DARUDAYU] Drink deeply of
the spirit of the Far East!
And then... choke on it!
[DARUDAYU] ♪ Hear the train blow
its whistle in the night ♪
[BOTH gasp]
[DARUDAYU]
Now, it is my turn to strike!
[MONSTER 11B roars]
[MONSTER 11B roaring]
[ALL gasping]
[CYAN]
Look at her go!
[SHUZO]
I am!
[DARUDAYU yells]
[ROSIA screams]
[CYAN]
Huh?!
[MONSTER 11B roars]
[DARUDAYU]
It is time for us to part ways.
Farewell!
[MONSTER 11B roars]
[DARUDAYU yells]
Someone help me!
[CYAN gasps]
It's Rosia?!
Darudayu, no!
You can't kill it!
[DARUDAYU gasps]
Why not?
[MONSTER 11B roars]
[CYAN]
Because...
I think... Rosia's in there.
[MAPLE]
King, I can't wait!
[GRATEFUL KING]
Yeah, it's finally time
for the deciding battle,
live at BooDooKan!
[MAPLE]
And we're not gonna lose.
[GRATEFUL KING]
To those young'uns?
Not yet! Great!
[BOTH]
Great!
[MAPLE]
Can I get another take?