[MONSTER 11A growling]
[CYAN]
Rosia! Is that you in there?
Please help me, Cyan.
[CYAN gasps] Hang on,
I promise I'll get you out!
[DAGGER] What are you
waiting for, you lazy slugs?
Go and capture Cyan, now!
[MONSTER 11A growls, roars]
[CYAN gasps]
[CYAN]
No, Rosia, don't hurt us!
[CYAN screams]
[CHUCHU]
Cyan!
[DARUDAYU grunts]
[CYAN]
Darudayu!
[DARUDAYU] Cyan, the time
is now! Believe in yourself!
Unleash the power
I know you have!
[CYAN]
But... I can't do it alone.
[SHUZO]
Don't worry. You don't have to!
[ALL yelp]
[CHUCHU]
Shuzo's helping!
[ROM]
Nice, Shu! Way to go, Buddy!
[SHUZO]
Heh, it's nothing!
[CYAN gasps]
You guys!
[DARUDAYU growls]
[DARUDAYU yells]
[DARUDAYU]
Cyan!
[CYAN grunts, gasps]
[CHUCHU]
You got this!
[RETOREE]
We're with ya!
[MOA]
Pyuru!
[CYAN]
I love you guys.
[MONSTER 11A roars]
[CYAN grunts]
[CYAN giggles]
[RETOREE, CHUCHU gasp]
[MOA squeals]
[groans]
Cyan, it's really you?
[CYAN]
Uh-huh. And look.
[ROSIA]
Huh? Girls, you're here.
[CYAN giggles]
[CHUCHU]
Hey, Cyan?
Wow, no way...
Cri-Cri were entirely--
They were inside
the dark monster!
[CYAN]
Mm...
[ROSIA]
No way...
Is... that really
where we've been?
Yeah, you were all taken in
and it was controlling you.
[gasps, whimpers]
I know why this happened.
It's because we were
so mean to you guys
and this was our punishment.
Guess I was already a monster.
[sobs] I'm sorry...
Mm-mm. It's cool. Can you stand?
[ROSIA]
Mm-hmm.
Way intense.
I'm so hungry.
Um, Cyan, I just want to say:
Thank you for saving
us from the monster.
We owe you big time.
[CYAN giggles]
You guys, I'm so
glad you're okay.
[gasps]
[ALL gasping]
[DAGGER laughing]
[yells]
My goodness!
I believe that is Dagger!
I hope not!
Another monster!
--[ALL whimpering]
--Just go away!
[CROWD screaming]
[ALL gasp]
[DAGGER chuckling]
You didn't behave yourself,
and now it's come to this.
You've forced my hand,
so this is my trump card.
[roars]
[laughs]
[gasps]
[DAGGER laughing]
[ANGELICA grunts]
President, let's get
a move on, please.
[MAPLE]
You're right. Moving on.
[CYAN whimpers]
[gasps]
--What is this?
--[ROSIA screams]
--[gasps]
--[whimpers]
[whimpers, screams]
Please help me!
Rosia, hang on!
Oh, crap!
We're caught like insects!
[DAGGER laughing]
Cyan!
[DAGGER]
You might as well face it.
You won't succeed no
matter how hard you fight.
I am in possession of the most
powerful song ever written.
Which makes me the music emperor
that Midi City must bow down to!
I've got it. We're goin' in.
[MAPLE]
Please be gentle.
[MAPLE] Careful, careful,
careful, careful, careful!
[sighs]
[MAPLE groaning]
[gasps]
The studio's at the
end of this hall.
--[alarm blares]
--[gasps]
[ANGELICA] Bad news.
It seems we've been discovered.
[MAPLE]
Well, of course we have.
You were as quiet
as a machine gun.
[ANGELICA]
We'll charge straight through!
[MAPLE]
Do the Hustle!
[gasps]
Oh, no!
[MAPLE]
How's that for bootylicious?
[DAGGER]
Midi City is full of Myumons
who live and breathe for music.
And now, they will only
be satisfied with yours,
and yours alone.
There is no higher honor.
Doesn't that make you happy?
No. That's not true happiness.
You see, I've already found it!
Yeah, that's right!
Cyan is a member of
Plasmagica and always will be!
Forget it, Fishface!
She's not going
anywhere with you!
Go away, and don't
come back, pyuru!
[DAGGER grunts] That's enough
out of you, Scum Queens!
[ALL scream]
Stop it, no!
[DAGGER]
Well, then?
[CYAN]
Jerk. This is a dirty trick.
Fine. You win.
I'll come with you.
Just stop it.
[ALL gasp]
--[ALL grunting]
--Aw, seriously?
[DAGGER chuckles] You have
indeed chosen wisely, Cyan.
About time you came
to your senses.
Now, for the contract.
[CYAN yelps, gasps]
[whimpers, screams]
[ALL]
No, Cyan!
--[DAGGER laughs]
--[CYAN screaming]
[GRATEFUL KING]
Rock 'n' roll, Baby!
[DAGGER gasps]
[screams]
What happened? We still alive?
[GRATEFUL KING]
Sorry to leave y'all hanging!
[CROW gasps, screams]
Is that guy-- No freakin' way!
It can't be!
It's the legendary rock guitar
god, my idol, Grateful King!
[ANGELICA chuckles]
You're safe!
Thank goodness, you're okay!
It's all better now, pyuru!
[ALL giggle]
[DAGGER]
Grateful King!
[gasps] He's still here?!
[DAGGER]
You're starting to irritate me!
[DAGGER roars]
[GRATEFUL KING gasps]
[DAGGER] I no longer
require your services.
Stay put and shut up.
It's unreal.
He has this much power?
[CYAN whimpers]
[DAGGER] A minor disruption.
Just ignore him.
Now, where were we?
That's right, about to
take over the world!
[roars]
[CYAN gasps]
[DAGGER roaring]
[ALL]
Look out!
[CYAN gasps, whimpers]
--[GRATEFUL KING groans]
--[CYAN whimpers]
[gasps]
[DAGGER]
King... You bastard!
[GRATEFUL KING]
Cyan!
Hey, kiddo, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have put you
in harm's way like this,
but I didn't think
I had a choice.
I know you can't stand fighting.
And more importantly, you
have a heart of pure gold.
That's what makes you so good.
[CYAN gasps] I know that
voice! It's so familiar!
Is that you, Mister Berry?
It's time to hit the road.
Because I refuse to put
you in danger anymore.
We have to say
our goodbyes, Cyan.
I gotta admit, the time I spent
with you was the coolest.
[CYAN gasps]
What are you doing?
[gasps]
Oh no, she just flew away!
She's going home,
back to her own world.
[RETOREE sniffles]
Okay, then...
We'll have to do our best to
take care of each other now.
[CYAN] C'mon, girls. Run away.
He's way too powerful!
[gasps]
Heh. Too bad, so sad, Dagger!
[DAGGER]
You wretch. I will end you!
[roars]
That goes for the
rest of you, too.
These are the last words
you will ever hear!
Okay guys, it's time to rally!
We're gonna take
back our Midi City!
[CYAN] Nothing's changed.
I'm still a 'fraidy-cat,
the way I've been a 'fraidy-cat
my whole freakin' life!
What was the point
of doing all this?
[DAGGER roars]
No! I can't go home! Not yet!
[GRATEFUL KING gasps]
[DAGGER]
What?!
I won't bail out and
leave everyone hanging.
Not this time!
Attagirl! Go, Cyan!
[DAGGER growling]
[roars]
Say goodnight, Dagger.
Show's over!
Evil has no place here!
[DAGGER yells, groans]
That was spectacular, Kitten!
Well done, my dear.
Is it over yet? Please?
[DAGGER]
Ow, my body!
[groans]
Oh, crap...
Ha! Well, isn't it ironic?
I guess you can't always get
what you want, now can you?
--Ya like it? Ya like it?
--[DAGGER] Ow! Ow!
[CROW screams]
--[CROW coughs]
--[DAGGER] Bite me, Hedgehog!
No, he's getting away!
Don't worry 'bout it.
He can't do anything now,
being the size of a pork bun.
[RETOREE]
Cyan!
[CYAN yelps]
You came back! If you
had really left for good
before I got to say
goodbye to you, I swear,
I would've hated you forever!
I'd never do that.
--[GRATEFUL KING] Cyan!
--[ALL gasp] Huh?
That was phenomenal.
You're a real rock star.
Thanks, Mister Berry.
[CROW] "Mister Berry"?
Who the hell is that?
She doesn't recognize the
legendary Grateful King?
[MAPLE] Uh... They're one
and the same, Genius?
[CROW]
What?
He transferred his own
soul into Strawberry Heart,
so that he could help Cyan and
all of you save Sound World.
In the flesh...
I am the rock candy, Momma!
[CROW gasps]
Leave him.
He'll get over it, maybe.
[AION]
It is a truth that shocks
even the only god
of the universe.
Clearly it is too much for a
rodent's tiny brain to process.
And hence, it's far too
cruel a reality for him.
Hey, Mister Berry-- Oopsie.
I mean, Mister
Grateful King, sir!
I, um, I just want to say
thank you for everything.
Because you...
Well, you were always
so encouraging to me.
Silly girl.
I'm the one who needs
to give mad props to you.
I'm really proud, Cyan.
You were brave.
No, that's not it.
The whole time, I was so scared.
But, you see...
I knew all my friends were here,
and that gave me the
strength I needed.
From my heart,
thank you so much.
Thank you, pyuru. Forever.
Yeah, Cyan. We love you.
Oh! Before I forget,
I have something.
[CYAN, RETOREE, MOA]
Hm?
[CHUCHU] Here! A present
from me to you girls.
Cool!
Guitar picks.
[CHUCHU]
You betcha!
You're even giving a pick to me?
[CHUCHU]
Of course, so we can all match!
Oh! It's so cute!
This means a lot. Thank you.
Sure!
[SHIBARIN]
We made it, but too late.
[POKOE groans]
Hakkun, the compass in your head
got messed up by the
city's magnetic field.
[HAKKUN gasps]
[POKOE]
Thanks to that,
we've been runnin' around
lost for three hours!
[HAKKUN] Sorry...
Midi City's big and scary.
[KITTSUN] Aw, the festival's
already over. This is the pits.
[OGASAWARA]
You're late, you amateurs!
[KITTSUN gasps]
[OGASAWARA]
Absurd.
I've been waiting almost
three hours for you!
[KITTSUN]
Oh, the weird guy!
[OGASAWARA]
Don't call me "weird guy"!
--It's Mister Ogasawara to you!
--[MAPLE] Oh, hi!
Where've you been
hiding, Chiseler?
All out of favors from Dagger?
You gonna try and make
a few dirty dollars
off of these innocent
young kids now?
[OGASAWARA] C'mon, you say
that like it's a bad thing!
[MAPLE] It is a bad thing,
you ham-fisted sociopath!
[music plays]
[ALL gasp]
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Ooh, hi, hi! ♪
All right, guys and gals!
Let's rock and roll!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Ready! 1, 2, 3, go! ♪
♪ Love life! Live it up!
We'll be very happy! ♪
[SHIBARIN]
The festival's still goin' on!
--[POKOE] We didn't miss it!
--[HAKKUN] Midi City's amazin'!
[KITTSUN]
C'mon, let's run for it!
[BOTH yelling]
[BOTH yelp]
[CROW]
Grateful King!
It's my ultimate dream
come true to jam with you!
[ROM] I'd intervene, but I
don't want to lose an eye.
[YAIBA] What he's doing
is incomprehensible.
I'm mortified just
looking at him. So hence--
[AION]
Poor puny rodent.
Your equally puny brain appears
to be melting from your skull.
I almost pity you.
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ And so we'll now always hope ♪
♪ and keep on dreaming ♪
♪ Never stop our singing ♪
♪ Passion flows non-stop ♪
♪ We're aiming for
an endless future ♪
♪ Nothing could be better,
the spotlight's shining ♪
[CHUCHU]
Cyan, thanks to you,
I've learned that even
music isn't as sweet
or important as true friendship.
[RETOREE]
Even if we're worlds apart,
we'll always be friends
no matter what, Cyan!
[MOA] I love Plasmagica
so much, pyuru!
And we wouldn't be the band
we are without you, Cyan!
[CYAN] I've always loved
everything about music.
But getting to play
it with you guys
made it the best it's ever been!
Oh, man! I want to stay with
you and keep playing forever!
[CROWD cheering]
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ One, two, three!
We'll echo around the world ♪
♪ And nothing we do
will ever be stopped ♪
♪ Let's climb on the notes
on the music staff ♪
[music continues]
[ANGELICA gasps]
President?!
In the flesh!
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Let's go journey,
no matter the time ♪
♪ We're laughing
while we're crying ♪
♪ We're giving all,
giving all out strength ♪
♪ Endlessly we're singing,
limitless performance time...! ♪
[CYAN]
Goodbye!
And thank you!
You're all the best, meow!
[music playing]
[CYAN inhales, exhales]
[CYAN]
Hi, I'm Cyan Hijirikawa.
First year, class 3.
I'd like to join the club.
Nice to meet you.
Nailed it.
[CYAN sighs]
I swore I'd do this today.
Hi, my name's Cyan!
I'm first year, class 3!
Very nice to meet you!
And I'd like to join the club!