So you're the
ultimate warrior, huh?
After lengthly investigation
and research,
I've finally arrived
at this truth.
According to this video,
the ninja master is the
world's ultimate warrior!
Legs the speed of
gusting winds...
Eyes that see through the
blackest darkness...
And the willpower to endure even
the most perilous situations!
Come forth and awaken, ninja
master! Kodama the Bedeviler!
Now go! Ensnare
Belldandy and her friends
into a melting pot of chaos!
We are born of the darkness
and ultimately we return to it.
And that... is the
fate of the ninja.
It seems like such a cruel
and sad law to live by!
Huh?
I wonder if that was a mouse...
I'm sorry I have
so much work to do.
But unfortunately,
I have no choice
but to get it all finished
by this weekend.
Because if you don't, you're
going to fail the class, right?
Uh. As a matter of fact, yes...
But the good news is I was
able to find this thing
just abandoned on
the side of the curb.
So, thanks to this computer,
I've made up a lot of ground
sorting this data.
It is a bit unusual
though, isn't it?
How is it possible
that someone would just
leave it sitting there?
I can't help wondering if the
owner is worried about it...
Well, not likely.
Considering it was thrown away.
Huh?
It's because newer
models keep coming out.
See, the reality is that
every two or three years,
everyone just goes out
and buys a new one.
I guess they just wanna keep
up with the newest technology.
I believe that this machine
found its way here
because it still
had so much to offer
and was destined to
come to you. In fact,
I think it's very happy to be
able to help you with your work!
Oh! You really think so? Hm?
Ah! The paper is jammed!
Oh, I'll get it!
This seems like something
you'd read in a manga, huh?!
What's my problem?
It's only her hand...
It's not like I've never
touched her hand before...
Only... her hand...
--Huh?
Ahhh! The printer!
I'm so sorry, but I wasn't
able to block it in time!
Oh, sorry about that...!
I guess my hand must've slipped!
You call that a "slip of
the hand," Skuld?!
Did you really think I'd let
you two get so warm and cozy
--that easily?
--What's that?
Oh, nothing!
Hm...
Hey, what's all that ruckus?
Keiichi picked up a bomb
with his bare hands
and blew himself up.
Not too bright!
Look, if you want to play
then go somewhere else!
I'm up against a deadline here,
and I'm REALLY busy right now!
Nyaaaah!
This is what you get for
trying to monopolize Big Sis!
Urd! Skuld!
How could they, of all people,
be giving my master
such a hard time?
Well then, it's time to go in.
But first, I suppose I'd better
do something about my size.
I will give you
an excellent taste
of the skill the ninja
master possesses!
Is it morning already?
Uh...?
Why, hello there.
AAACK! Who the heck are you?!
Oh dear. And you were
so great last night, too.
AAAHH... I've never
seen you before!
I was only joking.
Huh?
The truth is, I'm actually a new
goddess who's been sent to you
from heaven in order to
bring you good fortune...
Now! Come to me.
That's it...
This will be the end of your
relationship with Belldandy.
My master will be
absolutely delighted!
Huh?
Hey! What's with the tail?
Aaack! How are you able
to see through my magic?!
Are you a ninja?!
Well, of course I'm not!
Now show me your true form!
Reveal yourself!
--What is it this time?!
--Stop it! Not there... Oh!
Good morning, Keiichi!
Are you ready for breakfast?
Ah.
Here's my chance!
Belldandy!
I am stealing Keiichi.
Your absurd
sub-elementary-school-level
romance with him is over.
I'm afraid you no longer
have any purpose here!
Keiichi!
Does this mean you don't want me
to stay here with you anymore?!
Do you truly feel that I am
no longer of any use to you?!
It's a lie, isn't it...?
Please tell me that this
is all just a horrible lie!
It's a lie! I swear!
She just made all that stuff up!
Oh, thank goodness!
Are you saying that you don't
even have the slightest doubt
after walking in
on us like that?!
I've decided that as long as
I live here with Keiichi...
I will trust him,
no matter what happens
or how terrible the
circumstances might seem.
Hm!
Ah!
I've heard enough
of your nonsense!
This absurd romance of yours is
even below kindergarten levels!
Nevertheless...
I've been exposed,
so I'm left with no choice.
This is the sacred
law of the Ninja...
It would be a disgrace
for me to return alive.
Wait, it would be a disgrace
to return to where Mara is?
What? How could you have known?!
Whaddya mean? It's obvious.
Mara's the only one who would
pull a crazy stunt like this!
Mm-hm.
If I've revealed that,
then I truly have no choice!
Now that you've said
my master's name...
you will have to die with me!
I would've liked to
see the conclusion of
my favorite TV series...
Aaaahh...!
Stop you fool
or you'll be caught in the
blast and blown to pieces.
Uh!
What am I saying?
Gggh...
What happened?
I sealed the explosion by
putting up a shield around it.
But more importantly...
Why would you do such a thing?
Well, it's just...
my mission was...
If you were to die, I think
there are people for whom
it would cause a
great deal of sadness.
But even if that were true...
Ninjas are born of the darkness
and ultimately return to it!
From this point on,
I can no longer continue
to live as a ninja!
--Ms. Kodama.
--Yes, ma'am?!
As a Goddess, First Class,
Unlimited License...
I hereby command you to not
throw your life away in vain!
Because all creatures
born into this world
have not only
the right to live...
but also an obligation to live
out their lives to the fullest.
But if I can no longer continue
to live life as a ninja...
then what was the point
of having been born
in the first place?
Uh?!
I think... it was so that
you could come here.
Ah... My Liege!
Aw, man...
What's taking her so long?
Kodama...
Ms. Kodama?
Uh?!
I was just wondering if
something was wrong?
Oh, no! Of course not,
Lady Belldandy.
I think maybe I just felt
a little chilly, that's all.
Oh, dear!
Perhaps I should go find Urd
and see if she might have
some medicine to help you.
Ah..! No, that's okay, really!
You see, I already have
some of my own medicine!
You do?
There's no way
I'm gonna take any of that
woman's crazy concoctions!
Please take care of yourself...
Because colds can be tough
to get rid of sometimes...
Let's go back inside and
I'll make you some tea.
How could such simple words be
filled with so much kindness?
My heart is
overflowing with warmth!
Heartwarming, heartwarming...
I can literally see the
warmth emanating from her!
You're as incapable of hiding
your emotions as ever, Kodama.
Did you really think you could
forget your duties as a ninja,
and assume an ordinary
life with these goddesses?
You'd first have to defeat
every last one of us...
or vanish from this world
before you could ever
escape our law of blood.
Oh, my! Who are you?
No way! I didn't even
detect her presence!
How could I have been
discovered by such a buffoon!
Huh? An assassin?!
Hyah!
Hikari! What are
you doing here?!
Maybe she wasn't a friend
of Kodama's after all?
Traitors...
Death unto traitors!
Unto those who break the Law!
Kodama the Bedeviler,
the deserter...
...must die!
Hikari the Flash...
She's a ninja master who was
made at the same time I was!
But this is the
fate of the ninja.
To survive, one mustn't
consider who the opponent is...
only how to defeat them!
It seems poor Kodama can't
keep up with my blazing speed!
Try this on for size.
Do you really think that
brute strength will
be enough to defeat me?!
Aaaahh! Stop it!
Hold it right there, Kodama!
Or this man might soon find
himself to be without a nose!
Now then, unless you want
him bleeding to death,
I suggest you drop
all your weapons.
You seem to be a little
confused, Hikari.
Lady Belldandy is
the only one I serve
and the only one I must protect.
So slice away if
you really want to.
Which is what I would
really like to say,
but it would only cause
Lady Belldandy immense sadness.
Is this satisfactory for you?
Where did you have all
those things hidden?
Wait a minute!
I'm afraid you'll have to
lose all your armor as well.
Fine by me.
Very good.
Now stay right there... okay?!
And prepare to die!
--Yes! I finally got her! Huh?
--Kodama!
A dummy? Damn!
She used her
substitution technique!
Huh?!
Her arsenal of weapons
were just a distraction
to make me overlook
that one knife!
I've been fooled by Kodama's
trickery from the very start!
I've been defeated!
Special technique,
Desert Needle!
Stop this!
Yes, my liege!
I thought I told you,
you are not permitted to
throw your life away, Kodama...
Remember?
Regardless of whether or not
you feel it is justified.
Okay?
Yes, my liege!
Huh?
I don't believe this...!
How can I allow myself
to bow before someone
who isn't my master?
But then...
perhaps there is something to
serving an even higher power.
They should've been
back by now...
I beg of you, Lady Bell...
Please forgive me for
being so small-minded...
I finally understand
how trivial I am.
Please allow me to stay here
in exile along with Kodama!
Hikari...
I do not expect you to forgive
my foolish actions and behavior.
However... as recompense
for my indiscretions...
I ask that I may be
allowed to serve you...
Huh...?
Oh, my alarm...
Huh? Oh, no!
Ah! Kodama?
Kodama, wait for me!
So... You think they're
gonna be all right?
I do...
It seems to me that those two
know exactly what they're doing.
Mm...
But then... why do
I feel as though
there's an alarm going
off inside of me as well?
Damn you! The Floral
Daze Technique?!
That was a close one!
I came way too close
to missing this show.
So that's what your
alarm was for, huh?
All right, listen up!
My favorite show,
Mr. Holmes, is on at five
and I have to watch it.
How unfortunate.
This program isn't
over until six o'clock.
You two are new here, and
you just barged in on us,
so you don't get to
choose what we watch.
That doesn't matter.
I was here first,
so I'm gonna watch
it through to the end.
Or would you rather we leave
it up to a majority vote?
Majority vote, huh?
Okay, fine with me!
Now who wants to
watch Mr. Holmes?
Me! Me! Me! Me! Me!
--Huh...
--Hm...
Okay... Who wants to watch
Ninpu Kamuri Gaiden?
I DO!
Me! Me! Me! Me! Me!
Hey, Urd. I'm gonna watch
Record of the World's Inventions
at five-thirty. Huh?
Then I guess you can watch it on
another TV in a different room.
No way!
This is the only color TV
we have in the house.
Well, unfortunately,
we've already claimed
this room for our own.
Then we'll just have to
decide by majority vote!
I was hoping you'd say that.
Okay, who wants to watch Record
of the World's Inventions?
Oh, brother. Not again...
This program has
been brought to you
by the following sponsors.
I'm so glad I got to see
this episode again...
Hey, Kodama?
Hm? What's up?
I've got a snack if you're
hungry. Here, you have it.
How heartwarming!
Here, we can each have half!
Uh, all right then...
Somehow it almost kinda feels
like the old days, doesn't it?
Uh-huh!
Well, I don't care what
anyone else thinks,
but I just don't
trust that girl.
I have to admit that
I share your concern.
Hikari does seem to be
harboring some ulterior motive.
Frankly, I don't really care
what her and her
friends are up to.
I just wanted to watch Record
of the World's Inventions!
You just don't know
when to give up, do you?
And just what is that
supposed to mean, huh?!
In any case, regardless of
what the truth might be...
it's not Hikari's fault.
Whoever sent her here
is the one to blame.
Each of us has both a light
and a dark side within them.
Even knowing where
she comes from,
I must believe in the
potential of her light side.
I do understand how
you feel, Belldandy.
But what would you do if you let
anything bad happen to Keiichi,
like it almost did today?
If it comes to that...
then I will protect him...
Even if it costs me my life.
Looks like the drug
has taken effect.
Before we were transformed,
we were just two young lab rats.
Our relationship spans
beyond our species
and even beyond
a simple friendship.
I even remember a time when
you split a roach in half
and we both shared it.
Here, Kodama.
You can have the
hind leg, if you want.
That's all right, Hikari.
Why don't you just
go ahead and eat it?
Oh, Kodama...
If only you hadn't broken
the ninja code and deserted
then things wouldn't have
turned out like this!
At least I can offer
you a quick death.
Here, we can each have half!
Even though a ninja is
forbidden from having emotions,
I can't help feeling
that my poor skills
weren't the only reason
I couldn't kill you.
The truth is that I've been
hesitant from the very start.
So you were still on guard and
didn't eat the doughnut, huh?
I shouldn't be surprised.
You truly are a
first rate ninja.
No, I'm a failure...
A failure, a deserter, and
a disgrace to the ninja clan.
Plus, I had planned
to let you kill me.
I figured that if you didn't...
the master would probably
kill you for failing.
Don't say that...
Please, Kodama...
It seems you have
failed, Hikari!
I know that voice!
The failure of your duties are
a disgrace to the ninja masters.
Aren't you...
I am extremely disappointed
in both of you.
I will be reporting the
course of all recent events
back to our master.
Now, sit back and listen to
the melody of your demise!
Go forth!
Destroy the traitors
and their friends!
Hey, stop them!
What's going on?!
Whoa there! Where do
you think you're going?!
Get off me! Stop it!
You jerks! NO!
Damn! I knew Hikari
was up to something!
If that's how she wants
to play it... Depth--
No, don't!
If you use such a high output
summoning spell, Urd,
then Keiichi could be...
Hey, Keiichi! Are
you all right in here?
--Keiichi!
Those born of the darkness
ultimately return to it.
Mmm! I can't hold
on much longer...
Keiichi! Keiichi!
Ah... I'm done for...
Now I'm hallucinating...
Oh, Keiichi!
I swore I'd protect you,
even if it cost me my life!
I promised...
...and I will...
--Belldandy!
--Big Sis!
--Aah!
--Ah...!
She's summoning
some kind of spell.
It's the most powerful
purification spell...
Ultimate Demon Destruction!
Belldandy, don't!
If you use that spell, then...
Aaaahh!
--Belldandy!
--Big Sis!
Keiichi!
Her seal managed to absorb the
majority of the spell's power
before it broke.
It seems that you almost did
throw your life away there.
Oh, Belldandy...
Even after all the
times you've told me
not to use such
high-power spells.
And don't think that
sweet little face of yours
makes it all right! Okay?
All right, you three...
Have you managed to get your
fill of fighting yet, or what?
As ninjas, the three of us
are bound by a law of blood!
In order to escape this law,
we must either vanish
from this world...
or we can just kill
each other instead.
It has to be
one or the other.
Is that so? But then...
since all three of you are
here right now... together...
Hm? Ah!
Right. There is a third
option, if you want it.
What is this crap?! I can't
believe what I'm reading!
Dear Master...
we three ninja masters...
hereby declare... our desertion.
Hm...
Hey, Big Sis!
There's a letter for you!
Huh? That's weird.
According to this, it says it's
from the Goddess Help Line...
Hm...? So, what does the
letter say, Belldandy?
It says we regret
to inform you
that your goddess license
has been suspended.
Hm?
WHAT?!
Well, it figures, right?
The two are thrown
into infinite space...
You're still not perturbed,
even now, are you, Keiichi?
Next time...
"Ah! It Doesn't Matter Where,
So Long As We're Together."
Because I'm with you.
Just keep your
distance, Keiichi!
You need to do more
than just be with her.