I, goddess who stands
at the seat of Order
over Heaven and Earth...
do command that you be released
from the Earthly ties
that now bind you.
Right. Now after you've
finished composing your spell,
you must focus all
of your attention
directly on the
object of your spell.
You'll then feel something
stirring deep within you...
And that feeling is
your power, Skuld.
My attention...
Oh!
Stirring within me...
Ah!
Ah... It's actually floating!
I did it! It worked!
Look, Big Sis! Look!
Now, don't ever forget
that feeling, all right?
Mm-hm!
Good after-- Whoa!
Hey, Skuld! There's
something weird out here!
Now stop that, Banpei!
I don't know what I'm
going to do with him...!
--I'll be back in a second.
--Okay.
Are you okay, Sentaro?
So why is her power
working all of a sudden?
Skuld's feelings of
affection are providing
a source of strength
for her right now,
and those feelings are
what's causing her powers
to start working.
So that means...
Oh, I get it! Then she's...
Right. She is a girl, after all!
Whoa!
Well? Pretty cool, isn't it?
Yeah!
It was cool how your
sister healed my bruise
the other day, too...
It's like you guys are
magicians or something!
We aren't magicians, you
big silly, we're goddesses.
Uh... Goddesses? Hm...
Ah, I get it... People from
other countries are so cool.
Hm? Stop staring.
Uh, I wasn't looking at you,
I was just noticing
what you were doing
and it's kind of amazing!
Not to mention a little weird...
Huh? What's happening?!
Hey, aaah! Hey, you better
do what I tell you to do!
Whoa! It's gonna fall! Whoa!
Whoa!
You okay?
Um, uh-huh...
I guess I blew it, huh?
Huh?
Ah!
Ah...! I'm sorry!
No... I mean thanks.
Mm-hm...
--♪ La, la, la... ♪
--Huh?!
Singing...
♪ La, la, la... ♪
♪ La, la, la, la... ♪
So cool...
She's beautiful... Who is that?
That's Holy Bell. You see, all
goddesses have their own angel.
Um... An angel, huh?
Ah! So does that mean you
have an angel, too, Skuld?
Oh, you don't, huh?
Even though you're a goddess?
Don't be ridiculous!
What are you talking about?
Of course I have one!
That's awesome!
So, what's your angel like?
Please be born now, Angel!
Mm...?
I guess Big Sis must've
been right when she said
it wouldn't work unless
I use my own power...
But... I'm positive
I'll be able to do it now!
At least I think I can...
In any case, please, Angel...!
BE BORN NOW!
I already promised Sentaro
that I would show you
to him tomorrow!
Not enough power,
that must be it!
I'll use the magical
power amplifier
that I made before, and...
No! That wouldn't
be my own power!
That's right, it's an egg,
so what it needs is body heat!
Oh, please... Please!
PLEEEEEEASE!
What else? Let me see...
What else could I do?!
Hey, what's with all the
commotion in here, huh...?
Can't you practice your
magic a little more--
Huh?
Oh... I see...
Do you actually think you
can hatch your angel's egg
just because you have
a little power...
--I swallowed it...
--Huh?
I SWALLOWED IT!
Swallowed... the egg?
Mm-hm...
NOOOO!
Just come to my room...!
--NO WAY!
--And I'll give you a dose
of some medicine. An
extra-strength vomit inducer...
That'll definitely
make you cough it up!
Bad things always
happen to people
who takes your
weird concoctions.
This is all happening because
you did something stupid
without telling anyone.
That's true...
Now, come with me this instant!
Please help me,
Big Sis! I'm in danger!
Something...
something inside me...
Ah! Skuld...!
Skuld...! Belldandy!
If the power of the angel egg
continues to spread
like this then...
Given the level of
her powers right now...
it's very likely that
they'll go out of control.
Yes. But if we're lucky
this could bring more good than
bad, and then perhaps she--
Nevertheless, Skuld's
in danger right now.
I think we should
plan to seal it.
But I'd still like to avoid
doing that if we possibly can.
Belldandy!
Skuld!
You must stay in control...!
Try not to be
overcome by the power!
Mm...
Here it comes.
Once it's out, we'll seal
it before it can take form.
Belldandy!
Right!
Here we go!
Okay!
No, Urd! Not yet!
Uh?
An angel... But it's just so...
TINY!
How wonderful...!
It looks as though
she has decided
to favor Skuld with her power.
Uh...! Ah...
Boy do I feel pooped... Huh?
What's wrong, Big Sis?
Oh, Skuld, I'm so
happy for you.
Huh...? What for?
Just take a look behind you.
Hm?
Oooh! Big Sis!
It's an a-a-a-angel!
Not just any angel...
This one's yours.
So this is my...
Nice to meet you... Angel!
Huh?
Oh, thank you...
Wow...! So this must
be your angel, huh?
Yep! That's right.
Her name's Noble Scarlet.
Nice to meet you...!
She's a whole lot smaller
than your sister's angel was.
So what can she do anyway?
Huh...? Uh, what do you mean?
Uh...
Guess I shouldn't
have asked that...
Well, she's my angel,
so she helps me out
in all kind of different
ways every single day!
In fact, I'm gonna show you
exactly what I'm talking about!
Well, you don't have to
force her to do anything
just for me...
Come on, Sentaro!
Come on, Noble Scarlet!
We're going out!
Here you go.
Now do your best.
Belldandy.
Huh?
Don't you think we should
have sealed her after all?
Well, the way things are now,
she doesn't appear to have
the power to get out of control,
and besides that,
she seems to be kind-hearted
and loyal to her master.
But that isn't what
I'm getting at...
Urd...
You're not still upset about
botching that up, are you?
It's not that big a deal, so
there's no need for you to--
Ah!
Ooh...
They kissed...
AAAHH! Ugh...
Man, I really wish that
thing wouldn't ring so loud!
--Skuld!
--Hm?
You have a call.
Sentaro's on the phone for you!
Huh?
Sorry to have you come out
here on such short notice,
but I was hoping you'd tune
it up for me one last time.
Right! Now it's perfect...!
So if you lose, you can't
blame it on the bike! Hm!
Okay, well, I'm gonna
go take it for a spin.
Sure!
Wow! It's perect!
Well, of course it is! I mean,
who do you think I am?
Skuld...
That's right! I'm Big Sis's
genius little sister...
--Hey...
--Hm?
I have a favor to ask you.
Huh?
I, um...
What's wrong?
I'd like it if... you would come
watch the race tomorrow...
and wait on top of the
last berm on the course.
Okay... but don't you want me
at the finish line instead?
Mm-mm.
That last berm is where
the dirt is piled the highest.
You can get a good view of
the whole course from there.
Okay.
If you'll wait there,
then I'll be able to see you
from anywhere, and then...
I'm sure I'm gonna win this!
Oh... yeah...
Mm...
Uh, well, then...
Ah!
Uh... I didn't mean to!
Th-That was just...
I'm, uh...
I gotta go!
What a rotten thing to do!
Sentaro went home, and I
wasn't able to make him
a real promise about tomorrow...
And now he probably
thinks I'm a weirdo...
Even worse...
he might hate me now...
Stay away! Leave me alone!
Just get out of here!
I see... So that's
what happened.
And that's why she chased
you out of her room, huh?
You were just trying
to help Skuld out
in your own way,
though, weren't you?
You poor thing... Well,
I hope you understand
that she doesn't
actually hate you, okay?
Just give her some
time to calm down,
and try going back
to her room tomorrow.
Well, she probably shouldn't
go in there empty-handed.
What do you mean?
I bet the ice cream parlor's
probably still open right now.
Noble Scarlet...
It's the Kanto Junior
Open Regional Qualifier
short track finals!
Here are today's riders...
Riding for Dart-RS -
Number Two, Satoru Hakozaki.
Riding for Misaki-Sile - Number
Fifty-seven, Yoshikazu Yamane.
From Nekomi City,
riding independent--
Number Eighteen,
Sentaro Kawanishi.
With Team Genghis Khan--
I'm not mad at you anymore.
However... the next time
you butt in like that,
you're going right
back into your egg.
Mm!
Ah, ice cream...!
I'll bet that was Big Sis
or Keiichi's idea.
So... the next time that
Sentaro comes over... Mm!
Hm?
Nah, there's really no
need for me to go now...
Besides, I'm sure Sentaro
feels the same way I do,
so you can just stop
worrying about it, all right?
Uh?
Noble Scarlet? It's okay!
Oh, I'd better put that ice
cream in the refrigerator,
since I'm not gonna
eat it right now...
Uh...
And it's Sentaro
Kawanishi in the lead!
Will he be able to break
away from the pack?!
Close behind is Hakozaki in
second, and Matsumoto in third.
Will this be our
finishing order?!
Uh-oh! Hold on!
Number fifty-seven, Yamane,
is starting to catch up
to the front runners!
He's really gaining ground!
Look at those kids eat up
that track, folks!
Aw, man... I shoulda
known she wouldn't come...
Oh, no! Something's
happened to Yamane!
Oh, no! How do I
get around this?
And an official is on the scene.
Is Yamane out for good, or will
is he able to get back up again?
Ahh!
Ohh! And Kawanishi's
also gone down!
The front fork's not bent.
Guess the wheel
hub's okay, too...
Now, lemme see...
The spokes seem to be--
--It's fine!
--Hm?!
We tuned up that
bicycle together!
That's why I said you'd
be sure to win the race...!
And that's why I won't
forgive you if you lose this!
Go get 'em, Sentaro!
She came after all...
Just you watch, Skuld!
I'll win with this
bike no matter what!
I mean... I have a goddess
and an angel behind me!
I can't lose!
One more to pass...
LET'S GO!
And now...
the winner of the MTB
Kanto Junior Open
Regional Qualifier is...
Sentaro Kawanishi!
--Yeah!
--Woohoo!
Mm...!
I guess...
I'll be heading home...
Huh?
Noble Scarlet?
I just... couldn't
help it earlier...
I didn't care if he
thought I was a weirdo,
I just didn't want him
to lose, that's all...
But anyway I'm glad,
because he won using equipment
that I help to fix up.
So it's okay, right?
Now let's just go home.
Huh...?
Uh...?
You're still here!
Mm...! Mm... uh... Ah...
She did it again!
Skuld?
Huh?! Um, yeah... uh-huh...
Thank you.
Huh?
I thought it was all over for
me after I took that fall...
but I was able to win because
you came here to support me.
Mm... yeah?
And... you looked after
my bike for me, too,
which makes me feel like
I didn't really win
on my own, so uh...
So I... want you to have this!
Huh...?! But, Sentaro,
that's your award and--
But I want you to
take it, Skuld, please!
Uh... But I...
Uh, sorry to interrupt
your moment,
but we do still have some
awards left to present, so...
Ooh-hoo!
Sorry! I'll get out of your way!
I can't believe
that Noble Scarlet!
But I guess I'll
let it go this time,
since she did bring
me that ice cream.
Thanks for the support today.
No problem! I'm just
sorry I showed up late.
Oh, one other thing, Sentaro...
Congratulations!
Okay... Thanks, Skuld.
See ya later!
See ya!
Huh?!
Big Sis? Urd? What's wrong?
Huh? What is this?
That's Noble Scarlet, Skuld.
No!
The thing is... angels
show absolute obedience...
They always do what
they're told without fail.
It can't be... It isn't...
because I told her I'd send
her back to her egg, is it?
But why...? I told
her I loved her!
I said I wanted
us to be together,
and that I always
wanted her by my side!
Yes... and I'm certain that she
felt the same way that you do.
But to have an angel, one must
understand one's own weaknesses
and have the strength
to face them.
Then why?
Why didn't you
ever tell me this?!
It's not something others
can get involved with.
Because your angel is
a reflection of yourself.
But you know what?
If you'll just hold on to
these feelings you have now...
when you are finally
strong enough...
I'm certain that Noble
Scarlet will come back.
Noble Scarlet!
I'm going out!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Now let's go!
Okay!
Hang on...
Where's Noble Scarlet?
Ah... Well... we won't be able
to see her for a little while.
Huh? Why not?
She said that if I keep on doing
my best to become more mature,
she'll come back to
see me again one day.
All right! Well, I sure
hope we get to see
Noble Scarlet some day soon.
Mm-hm!
It's all because I
told her to get lost...
Don't worry about it.
We were all worried.
I'm sorry.
It was all my fault...
Next time, "Ah! I'm half
goddess, half demon?"
Some people are too
innocent for their own good.
Uh, who're you talking about?