Morisato...
Can you hear me?
Are you there?
Who's there?
Is that you, Keima?
I mean, Hotarunosuke.
What is "fate"?
Ever since I met Belldandy...
I've wondered that
from time to time.
Maybe the dream
I had that night...
is a sign of something to come.
--Keiichi?
--Hm?
Are you up?
Yeah...
Good morning, Keiichi!
Did you sleep well?
Morning, Belldandy...
Uh, yeah, I did. Huh?
Hey, wait a minute. That's--
I came across this when
I was doing some cleaning
and going through old boxes.
It's my grandfather's journal!
Oh... So his name was
Hotarunosuke, huh?
He certainly was more
handsome than you.
Oh, put a lid on it, will ya?
Who's that girl in
the picture with him?
Hm... The photo's a little worn
so I can't make
her out very well...
Maybe it's my grandmother...
Hm?
A map.
Hey! There's something
written on it.
"My life's luster has been
left here at this location."
It's... it's a...
What does that mean?
--All right, Keiichi...
--Huh?
I'd say we're ready to go!
What? Go where?
Whenever there's an X on a map,
it obviously means that
there's buried treasure
somewhere, silly!
Clearly a magnificent
adventure awaits us all!
You guys watch too
much television.
Look, the Auto Club's camping
trip is right around the corner,
so I don't have
the time or the money
to go on a treasure hunt.
Oh, boo! You're such
a bore, Keiichi!
Say what you want, but it's not
going to make any difference.
--Oh, Mo-ri-sa-to!
--Huh?
Hey!
Eh?
Eh?!
And so, let the Nekomi Tech Auto
Club's Power Up Camping Trip...
...begin!
YEAH!
So, why'd you decide to
come camping too, Chihiro?
Well, isn't it obvious...?
Because it looked like
a lot of fun, of course.
Yeah, I thought you'd say that.
What's wrong?
You don't think the sponsor
who generously funded
this trip should attend?
No, I don't think that...
Well, thanks...
I'm very glad to hear it.
This sure is a stylish mansion.
Yeah, it's great! I heard
the owner was actually
an acquaintance of my
grandfather's. So when I called,
he said he would rent
the place out cheap to us.
Hey Belldandy, do you feel it?
Yes, I do... I feel a
definite presence here.
There's something... in there.
Uh, hello...? Anyone here?
It's Keiichi Morisato...
There is something here.
If it's a demon...
I'll take it down!
Hm?
I've been waiting for you.
Welcome to Honda Manor.
I'll be your host.
My name is Chieko Honda.
I'll be taking care of you.
Uh... come again?
Oh. Well thank you
very much, Ms. Honda.
Uh, yeah!
Thanks for your help.
Huh?
Oh, Master Morisato!
HUH?!
You remembered our
promise, didn't you?
Oh, thank you.
Um, I'm sorry but I really don't
know what you're talking about.
Uh...
Morisato!
You scum.
Well...
You're quite the little stud,
aren't you, Keiichi?
And when you already have
my big sis... How could you?!
No! You've got the wrong idea.
I swear, this is some kind of--
AAAAAAHH!
No, It can't be. I just don't
see how that could be posible.
Have you really forgotten
about our promise?
What promise have
I forgotten about?
I'm pretty sure this is the
first time I've ever met you.
The first time we've met...
Then you've forgotten me, too?!
I'm sorry, but I
just don't think that
you and I have ever met before.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry!
Are you all right, Keiichi?
Excuse me, but can
you please tell me
what your relationship
is to that girl?
Well, um... Our
relationship is, uh...
Regardless, it doesn't matter,
whether you can
remember it or not
the two of us made a promise
to each other a long time ago!
Uh... I'm kind of
at a loss here...
Morisato!
It's time for us to start
the Auto Club meeting.
Aren't you guys finished with
your lovers' quarrel yet?
I don't know if that's
what you'd call it.
Look, it's already
getting dark outside,
so why don't we just leave
it at that for today?
Then I shall get your dinner
ready for you right away.
I can help you prepare it
if you would like.
That's not necessary!
That girl is a remnant.
I know...
I realized that
as well just now.
Then why aren't
we doing anything?
There's something that
concerns me about her.
Hold on!
--Hm?
So what exactly is a remnant?
When someone departs this world
and leaves behind a strong
emotional sentiment...
those feelings can take
on a physical form.
That's... what a remnant is.
So... So you're saying
she's a ghost?!
Well... yeah...
something like that.
I'm going home!
The Auto Club's Camping Trip
meeting is now called to order!
Take it away, Dai.
Right. Number thirty-six, Otaki,
will now sing you
his greatest hits.
YEAH!
Hoo boy...
♪ The blood in my veins
is the vaseline of my soul. ♪
♪ I'll put my life on the line,
put the pedal to the floor. ♪
No, master, you mustn't!
Oh no, it's okay.
[chattering]
Hey, over here!
Woohoo!
Are you all right?
Huh?
You know, you've had an
awful lot to drink tonight.
Maybe you should
take a little break?
I just can't remember,
no matter how much I try.
Are you positive
it was really me
that made some kind of promise
with you a long time ago?
Huh?!
Where did you get
a copy of that photo?
But that's impossible.
Who are you...?
Was is just my imagination?
Hey, Belldandy...!
Are you listening or what?
Yes.
I was saying...
...that I finally decided
to open my own shop
and live my life
the way I want to.
These are good... Here!
You want one?
All right, thank you.
The seasoning in
these potatoes...
Hey, Morisato, where are you?
Are you, like,
makin' out with Belldandy
in some closet or
somethin''? Hic!
You've had a little
too much to drink...!
You just saw Big Sis
with the others
at the party a minute ago!
Huh?
AAAHHH! YEEEAAAHH!
--Huh?
Oh, no! That's Skuld!
I can't find the remnant
or Keiichi! Come on!
Right!
[cheering]
We never should've let
them out of our sight.
Be on your guard... She might
try to possess Keiichi.
She wouldn't!
Don't be so naïve!
A remnant will do
almost anything it takes
to achieve its goal.
Skuld! Miss Hasegawa!
This is the room, isn't it?
Thankfully, they're
only unconscious.
My unbinding spell
isn't working.
Hey! Open this door!
We know you're in there!
Give it up, and come
out here right now!
It's no use.
That door will not open.
Now then, I need you to think
back and remember that day...
Try to remember the promise
we made to each other.
Listen... You must
fulfill your promise.
AAH! They're ghosts!
Oh, look who's talking!
AAAH!
Urd! Since remnants are
different from demons...
the usual anti-demonic
programs won't work.
Please... Grant me the wish
that you once promised.
If you don't, then I'll
never be able to let you go.
Stop this...!
I know it's hard to believe, but
he's not who you think he is!
STOP IT!
That is Keiichi Morisato
that you're holding!
I assure you,
he's not Hotarunosuke,
who I know you've been
waiting for all this time!
That doesn't matter
to me anymore...
I can't wait any longer.
My encounter with
Master Hotarunosuke...
lasted for only
four summer days.
I met him while I was being
treated for an illness...
and he made a promise to me.
Even when I was on my sickbed...
that promise gave me
strength and hope.
When I eventually left
this world... I still waited.
And then... after so
many years had past...
he finally came to see me.
Even though it's a
different time, I knew...
that it... was fate.
Please tell me...
What was the promise
you that made long ago...
with Hotarunosuke?
Uh...? What happend?
I must have drank way
too much last night.
Good morning, Keiichi!
Did you sleep well?
If you don't mind...
there's something I'd
like you to have a look at.
What would you want to show me
down here in the basement?
Huh?! Aren't you...
And isn't this a...
A Brough Superior!
But then... what's it doing in
a place like this...? Huh?!
It can't be!
Yes.
It seems that it broke down and
was left here many years ago.
This motorcycle once
belonged to your grandfather.
And as for her...
It would mean a great deal
to me if you could repair it.
In fact, I don't even mind
if you keep this motorcycle
after it's been fixed.
But... before you take it away,
I was hoping you'd give me
a ride around the lake...
if it wouldn't be
too much trouble.
Since that was the promise
Master Hotarunosuke made to me.
You've waited decades...
just to take that ride...
This whole time... you've just
been waiting here, haven't you?
Because I knew you'd
return someday...
Maybe I can fix it.
Whoa!
That freakin' bike is...
...the so-called
"Rolls-Royce" of motorcycles!
It's the legendary
Brough Superior!
All right...!
We can use this bike to help
rebuild the Auto Club finances!
This bike's a treasure that's
definitely worth repairing!
I can see these guys are
gonna be a bit of a problem.
Um, excuse me!
Huh?
Please don't take
this the wrong way...
but I need to repair
this bike on my own.
What'd you just say?!
Morisato, you little rat!
Don't tell me you're thinking
of hoggin' it all to yourself?!
Quiet!
So. Why exactly do you
feel the need to
fix this bike all by yourself?
Well... That's a little
hard to explain,
but I just have to
do it that way.
I guess you could
say it's my fate.
It's your fate, huh?
Well, there's no arguing that.
Tamiya! Otaki!
Oh!
My chronic abdominal spasms!
Are you okay, Den?!
C'mon, this way.
What? What was that?!
Wait a minute... where was
he hiding all that stuff?
Morisato.
Huh?
Just about every
motorcycle from that era
was like a unique
model unto itself.
They've got a lot of
peculiarities, so watch out.
I will.
Well, see ya later.
Uh... Thanks again
for your help!
How long are you
gonna sulk over this?
Well, it's totally
embarrassing for a goddess
to let herself faint after
seeing a mere remnant...
You gotta keep your chin up
and not let it get to you.
After all, you may
be a mighty goddess,
but you're still just a kid.
SHUT UP...! I TOLD YOU
NOT TO CALL ME THAT!
I HATE YOU, YOU BIG DUMMY!
Yeah, yeah...
So. How's he doing?
I was thinking... there's
still one thing I don't get...
How did you figure out
that there was a connection
between her and
Keiichi's grandfather?
Because of the seasoning
on her yummy potatoes.
"Potatoes"?
I noticed it in the flavor
of the boiled potatoes
she served us.
It was exactly the same
as the seasoning recipe
that Megumi had once given me.
So they had the unmistakable
"Morisato flavor"?
I suppose...
But I was also tipped off
by the map and photo, as well...
That's just like you.
Oh, my, my... Aren't you
just a little bit worried?
At this rate, she'll steal
Keiichi from you in no time.
It's all right.
The truth is, I think I might
understand how she's feeling.
Keiichi and I might someday
be separated, as well.
Belldandy!
C'mon, RUN!
We're going for one more lap!
I'm gonna croak!
Man, those two
are totally spent.
I can't believe they're
still standing...
Just leave me alone!
I don't want to!
Aw, c'mon, Skuld!
Hey, you don't have
very many channels here.
You're interfering
with my cleaning!
The laundry dryed
quite nicely today.
Here. Why don't you
take a little break?
Why should a goddess
have to do push-ups?
And then next you
add the heavy cream.
Oh, I see...
This one here is
far more efficient.
--Hm...
--Ah...
It seems that this
part is hurting.
Uh-huh...
Well, I'm all done.
Now we'll be able to take
it for a ride tomorrow.
Thank you for all
your hard work.
Hey, I was wondering...
Can I ask you about something?
Sure, what is it?
Well, I think that my
grandfather, Hotarunosuke,
really did want to
come back here, but,
for some reason, he
just never was able to.
And because of that...
you ended up waiting
around here for him
for so many decades.
Do you ever think it
would have been better
if you guys had never
met in the first place?
When I was sick in bed...
I did feel some
resentment towards him.
I wondered why he
didn't come visit me.
But in spite of that,
I couldn't stay angry.
Because I still felt that
meeting Hotarunosuke
was still the brightest
moment of my entire life.
So you see...
I'm sure it's better
to have met him
and suffered this fate...
than to have passed him by
and never known him at all.
I guess I'll know
after tomorrow's ride
whether or not I was right.
Well, we'll be back
in a little while.
All right.
Be careful, okay?
Well, there they go at last.
Uh-huh.
All right... Well, have a look.
Mm.
The soft breeze...
The pleasant hum
of the engine...
And the scenery from a
completely different perspective
than when you just
walk along the road.
This is what you wanted
to show me, isn't it?
Back when I feared
the shadow of death
as it loomed so near.
The trees. The earth. The sky.
And myself...
We all share a common
fate in how we'll be
swept away in an
instant on this breeze...
And yet... That's
the very reason...
I'm so happy I got to meet you.
On this breeze that blows
only here and now...
Master Hotarunosuke...
Thank you, Keiichi.
Huh?
For being so patient with
me and all my demands.
Oh, it's not like that!
I mean, well... Huh?
Farewell...
I think that's what
she whispered to me
at the very last moment.
--Our treasure...
--Oh, Den!
C'mon you two, stop crying!
Are you really just going
to leave that thing here?
Yeah.
Y'see... I think I saw a
bit of myself in the situation
she was faced with.
There might come a time when
I'll be just like her...
When I'll have to wait
patiently for Belldandy
to return to me from heaven.
Oh, Keiichi...
That's why I want
to leave it here...
For her...
I promise that I won't
keep you waiting
for years and years like that.
Well, that's a relief!
But I have been
wondering what I would do
if that ever did happen.
What do you think you would do?
I guess I'd just...
keep working on my bike,
and hope you would eventually
come back to me someday.
And then... if we were
able to meet again...
I guess I'd at least be able
to take you for a ride.
We could ride all
around Nekomi...
the place where I met you...
and so many others...
Keiichi... I'm so
glad we came here.
And so... in the basement of
the old hotel on the hilltop...
you can still find a
Brough Superior motorcycle
continuing to sleep
the time away.
That's right. I'd be glad
to tell you any time...
letting the melody carry
my infinite feelings to you.
But I...
Next time: "Ah! The Song of
Love That Shakes the Heart"
I love you!
--I l-l-lo...
--Oh, just spit it out!