Ah, a date with
his girlfriend, huh?
Honestly, what's taking so long
for this relationship
to heat up?
Oh, Skuld, it's so sweet
that you like this stuff.
They go to the movies...
and out for a walk
in the park...
and then a love rival
suddenly appears.
Oh... I see.
Well, I guess it's
all for the best...
I've got to get the next one...
I'm home!
Huh?!
Ah...! Keiichi's home,
how wonderful!
Welcome home!
Listen...
Yes, dear?
Look, it's fine if you wanna
come greet me when I get home...
but this is a bit too much.
Why...? Is this
not to your liking?
Belldandy!
I see you were so hungry
you came running out
to meet us, Peorth...
I'll go make something
for you right away.
Belldandy!
You mean you two were together?
--Yes.
--This is...
You really are a
nuisance, aren't you?
I can see that Keiichi
has finally been able
to warm up to you, Peorth.
Eh... HUH?!
--Why, you...
--You've got the wrong idea!
So, if it's all
right with you...
I think it would
be a wonderful idea
for you to stay here
with us for a little while.
What?!
I... guess you're right!
All right, Keiichi...
Eh?!
I want you to give
in to your impulses
and tell me what your wish is.
Ah...! That tickles!
Cut it out...!
You look so happy, Keiichi!
I'm telling you you've
got the wrong idea!
I am fully prepared to remain
right here with you...
for as long as it takes
to hear what your wish is.
Well... I'd certainly
like to be able to
grant that wish for
you, Peorth, but I'm...
Huh?!
Oh! I can't believe
this is happening!
You're going to grant
MY wish, Keiichi?!
Huh?!
Wonderful! I can feel
your love, Keiichi!
You completely misunderstood!
I shall tell you...
what my true heartfelt wish is.
You've got it all wrong!
I'd like... to go on
a date with you tomorrow.
A... date?!
Ah...!
It's ten A.M. now...
I am waiting for him
at the water fountain
by the train station...
I have arrived at the appointed
rendezvous thirty minutes early.
I have arranged
everything to perfection.
For my research has proven...
that the way to guarantee
romantic encounters...
is by making plans for
indisputably
romantic situations!
We'll go enjoy a
romantic film...
So lovely...
Like your glistening tears.
Oh!
We'll drift through a world of
enchantment at the aquarium...
And that fish... is
called a "scribbled toby."
It's amazing...
And then, to a park
to watch the sunset.
Come back here, you!
Try and catch me!
I've got ya now!
And that night, when our
passion reaches its peak...
--Keiichi...
--Peorth...
It's a magnificent plan! And
there's not a single flaw in it!
Sorry! Did I keep you waiting?
He's here and he's
sorry for being late...
And then I... Right!
That's okay.
HUH?!
Uh... Hey.
Hi!
Wha... What is going on here?!
Well, it's a long story...
I thought that going
on a date was defined as
a man and a woman...
being alone together!
Yeah, well I think this
is more what you'd call
a "group outing."
Uh...
Well, of course
that's what it is!
If we're at all in
the way, we could just--
Yes, you certainly could!
Why don't you just
run on home now
and start getting dinner
ready or something, okay?
I guess that would
be for the best...
Actually, I think
it would be more fun
if we all went together!
Well, if you really
think so, Keiichi...
After all, there's no telling
what would happen to me
if I were left
alone with Peorth.
A "Group outing," he calls it!
What kind of excuse is that?!
Well, I won't let him lay
a finger on my Big Sis!
It was a pretty clever idea for
Keiichi to have come up with.
This could get interesting...
It's just no use...
If I get upset now,
all my preparations
will go up in smoke!
Huh?
Well, now that we've got
everything settled...
What do you think we should do?
Now you just leave that to me!
You see, I have a
meticulously thought out plan.
Now this is the correct
way to start off a date!
Oh...!
They're screening
this romantic film.
I'm sorry...
but I don't think I
have quite enough money
to cover everybody's tickets...
And what exactly were
you planning on doing
on our date today, Keiichi?
I, um...
Excuse me...
Huh?
I received these tickets
from the newspaper people.
So why don't we just use these?
Whoa! Way to save
the day, Belldandy!
So I'll have to watch
out for her after all...
Curse you, Devil King Sauce!
I'm toast, Pastry Man!
It looks like...
I'm going to be eaten alive!
No! Don't be ridiculous,
Jelly Doughnut Girl!
Well, this is
technically a film...
but it sure is a long way
from being romantic.
Keiichi...? Could we leave now?
Huh...?!
That was pretty
darn good, wasn't it?
It was so exciting!
Pastry Punch!
Bwa-ha-ha!
That old technique won't work
with the Devil King Sauce!
Grr...! Pastry Punch!
This is totally unacceptable...
Aagh! You got me!
We're going to the aquarium!
--C'mon!
--Hold on!
Looks like we lost them.
Excuse me...
Actually, I also received some
free tickets to the aquarium
from the rice vendor.
Uh...
And what on earth could
possibly be romantic about this?
It's shell is so hard
and it's body is so soft!
I think it's cute!
I do not have time
for all these people!
I have got to ditch them--
Peorth?
Huh?!
Thank you so much for organizing
an afternoon of fun activities
for all of us!
I think it's wonderful
that we're able to get
along so well together!
Peorth?
I see all these years haven't
changed you for the better.
Honestly... You're a
silly bothersome fool.
Peorth?
And now Storm of
Roses technique!
Peorth, no!
Whooaa!
Keiichi!
Belldandy!
Hey... what the heck
has gotten into you?!
Are you okay?
What is it?
--All right... here you go!
--Ah, thanks!
Hey, Keiichi! Get away from her!
What're you doing?!
Oh, no you don't!
I'M gonna be the one
that sits next to Big Sis!
--Hey, get a grip!
--You're hungry, aren't you?
Move it!
Come on!
You have my thanks, Peorth.
What are you pouting
about over here?
Uh...
Do you really want to be
alone with Keiichi that badly?
Of course I do!
I mean, it is my mission,
in case you've forgotten.
And that's the only reason?
Why... whatever are
you trying to say?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Oh, never mind.
I'm saying this direct
approach you're trying
will never work
against Belldandy.
She'd be able to find him in
a crowd of a million people...
or if you took him far away.
She would go to the
ends of the Earth.
Because that's the
way Belldandy is.
Keiichi!
I know that... all too well.
Mm...
Well... all right then.
If that's how it is,
then I'll change my strategy.
I knew she'd take the bait!
I can't allow her to do
anything out of my sight now,
not when this is just
starting to get interesting.
Pool tickets?
Oh... are those for the
indoor pool that just opened?
That's right, Skuld. Why don't
we all go there together?
Oh...! That just sounds
like so much fun!
Just you watch, Belldandy...
That's the spirit.
Come to think of it,
I'm a really lousy swimmer.
What the heck am I
supposed to do now?
Keiichi!
You're totally
turned on right now.
Don't worry, that's good!
It's perfectly natural.
Stop ogling at my Big Sis with
that dirty look in your eyes!
Ah...
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Even for a goddess, my looks
truly are extraordinary.
Keiichi definitely won't be able
to take his eyes off me now!
Huh?
You dress like that
all the time, Peorth,
so it's really not a big deal.
Yeah, that outfit's nothing new.
Fine then. Joke about it
now, while you still can!
Hmph! For I have already
discovered the crucial fact
that Keiichi doesn't
know how to swim.
I'll push Keiichi
into the water...
and then rescue him
just before he drowns.
After that, some mouth-to-mouth
resuscitation will be in order.
And once he's come to...
I'm sorry... I was
mistaken about you, Peorth.
Oh, Keiichi!
Yes, Keiichi...!
I shall soon set you free
from your terrible agony!
I was just wondering...
Are you going to be here
a little while longer?
Uh, well... yeah.
I'm going to buy some
drinks right now...
but would you be interested
in some swimming practice
after that?
Um, no thanks... I really
can't swim very well,
so don't worry about it, okay?
Oh, that isn't what I meant.
Ah!
You see... I really want to go
swimming with you, Keiichi.
You mean that? Sure!
Well, I'll go buy
us some drinks then.
I'll be right here!
Big Sis! I'm coming with you!
This is my chance!
Belldandy!
Keiichi?
Huh?!
Waah!
--Now all I have to do is...
--Keiichi!
Soar high O, Spirits of water!
Hm?
Aaaahhh!
Mm...
Uh?
Mm!
What do you think you're doing?!
I'm so sorry! When I
was rescuing Keiichi,
I accidentally drove the
water spirits out of control,
and I was afraid that the
spirits might have poisoned you
in the process...
I was just trying to extract
some of the water spirits
that were inside you...
I'm just glad that
you're all right now!
Not again!
Let's do our very
best today, all right?
Belldandy.
I hereby challenge you...
to a Level Three Goddess Duel!
Huh?
Did... she say "A Level
Three Goddess Duel"?
Yes. Long ago, it was a contest
once practiced in Heaven.
However it has fallen into
disuse for quite some time now.
Why are you doing this, Peorth?
If you win, I am
prepared to return
immediately to the
Earth Help Center
knowing my license
will be suspended!
But, Peorth!
However, if I am the
winner of the duel...
you must allow me and Keiichi
to go on a real date,
where only the two
of us are present.
How stupid! There's no way
Big Sis will ever agree
to a dumb wager like that!
Very well then.
Huh?!
I accept.
But Big Sis!
Now, in accordance with
the time-honored rules,
we will begin the first match.
Each of you--
bring out your angels!
And, GO!
HUH?!
I guess this is why
the first match
has never been all
that popular...
The winner is... Belldandy!
That's my Big Sis!
Match number two!
The Fish-Smacking Game!
No...! I just can't do it!
Boo-yah!
My poor Big Sis...
The winner is... Peorth!
Well, kids... everything so
far has been a warm-up...
Now it's time for the real
show... The Meteor Strike!
The first one to hit
the target is the winner!
Did I mention that
this round's projectiles
will be actual meteors
hurtling towards the Earth?
Belldandy... I will
emerge victorious.
We shall see...
Wait a minute!
Did she just say "METEORS?!"
Yeah, so what's the big deal?
And begin!
If something like that
really fell on us...
Um, please excuse me...
Huh?
Peorth, it is you, isn't it?
Belldandy!
So you must be the one
who's going to be helping me
fix the bugs in
the subsystem, right?
I'm honored to be
able to work with you!
And it's an honor
for me as well...
But you should know,
I will not be outdone.
Let's do our very
best today, all right?
It's no use...!
I cannot determine
the bug's location!
It seems the bug has
merged with the virus...
creating a counter-current!
OHH!
Peorth! Peorth!
Peorth! Thank goodness...
The damage isn't all that bad.
But, what about the bugs?
It's all right now.
I was able to dispose of
them... thanks to your help.
Huh?
Thank you again for
your help, Peorth.
It was a total shock.
That I, of all goddesses, not
only allowed a bug to get by me,
but I actually passed out.
Even more shocking
to me, was the fact that
this event was recorded
as a team effort
between the two of us.
Why would she do that?
What made her want to
show me any sympathy?
Uh... Belldandy?
Are you all right?
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to
scare you like that, Keiichi.
That's the way Belldandy is.
I tried to tell you.
Well, I simply cannot
stand her arrogant,
hypocritical attitude
for one minute longer!
So you really were holding
a grudge against her.
Huh?
I may not look it, but I happen
to be a system administrator.
Peorth...
Huh?!
This is regarding that time
when you two were fixing
bugs in the subsystem, huh?
Isn't there something you want
to say to Belldandy about that?
Something you want to say?
Belldandy...
I don't understand why
you couldn't have just
taken credit for
that task on your own.
You probably meant well by it,
but I did not want your pity--
not then, and not now either!
Ah!
What is it?!
I'm so glad that's all it is...
because you've made
an unfortunate mistake.
Huh?!
You see,
the reason I was ultimately
able to find the bug back then
is because it
had gotten inside you.
That's why that job
truly was a joint effort
between the two of us!
But... That's so...
Silly. Yes, get it now...?
It means your petty, long-held
resentment was unjustified.
Oh, man! What a lame
reason to hold a grudge!
Oh, Peorth...
Belldandy...
this whole thing could end up
being a lot of trouble for us.
Oh, it's all right!
Don't worry.
Skuld will take
care of this mess.
What?!
Oh! Are you okay?
Peorth?
Heh. Looks like she dozed off.
Ah, I see. So that's
what that means...
Please, Skuld! Stop whining,
--and start helping!
--Aw, man!
Good grief, what
a piece of work...
Why don't we just
dump her over there?
We can't do that, Skuld!
Then stop complaining
about how heavy she is!
Oh, be quiet. It just
slipped out, that's all.
One little joke.
Ah, so she really is heavy then!
Going for a walk at a seaside
park and watching the sunset...
It's not quite what I
had in mind, though...
Well... at least
one wish came true,
so I guess I'll leave
it at that for now.
Thank you, Belldandy.
Hey Urd, how did you know
about that stuff anyway?
Ah, well, one time
I got into Peorth's files
purely by accident--
Hey! That's a major
violation of the rules!
It's water under the bridge.
Why is it I still remain
here on the surface world?
If you were only here
to grant a wish,
you'd have gone back already.
Next time, "Ah!
I Just Can't Say It."
Hey, Peorth, let me
finish talking, will ya?!