Well, let's go check it out!
Yeah!
Man, we're gonna eat
a whole lotta free food!
This is a pretty high class
end-of-the-year party
we've got ourselves invited to!
It's not a year-end party,
it's a Christmas party!
Holy cow, Sayoko's
house is enormous!
I'm getting' kinda
nervous going in now.
Oh, it'll be just fine...
After all, the invitation
did specifically say
it was okay for us to
bring guests along.
And besides, Miss Sayoko
is such a wonderful person.
Okay.
So you think we should
head in now, too?
Sure!
All right...! Time to eat!
That's Sayoko for ya...
She never said anything about
the party being formal attire.
I am sure she simply intended
the party to be come as you are.
Just what I'd expect of an
international conglomerate!
Hey, Keiichi...
Have you seen Tamiya
and Otaki around lately?
No, I haven't seen
them for awhile...
Our first target has
now been demolished.
Right...! Time to mount our
assault on the next cuisine!
Wait for me, Den!
Do they really have to be
like that ALL the time?
Hey! Aren't you gonna
drink that, Keiichi?
Hey, that's mine!
Get your own!
Aah...!
Ah! Urd, you have
the worst manners!
In fact, your crude
behavior makes it
embarrassing to be a goddess!
Ugh...
We greatly appreciate
your patience.
Miss Sayoko Mishima will now
be making her grand entrance.
Yep, she's as much of
a show-off as ever...
I would like to extend
a very warm welcome
to the Mishima Group's
annual Christmas party.
This is just a modest
party I'm hosting,
but I hope you all
have a wonderful time.
We have several varieties
of entertainment lined up
for your amusement
this afternoon.
So as the organizer
of today's event...
my hope is that you will all
thoroughly enjoy yourselves!
I doubt she actually organized
this whole thing herself.
Hey, why don't go on out there
instead of standing in
the corner like this.
Okay!
Now the real show begins.
Oh, Belldandy?
Huh?
Would you mind coming
up to give me a hand
entertaining the guests...
It'll help get
our party rolling.
I would be more than happy to.
Just as I thought...
Sayoko's cooking up
some kind of scheme.
If my helping out will allow
everyone to enjoy themselves,
I would be glad to help
out any way that I can.
Now I have her...
And I've got the
home field advantage.
That's right, everyone here
is already on MY side!
Today, you will taste
the bitter agony of defeat.
Well then, let's begin...
Naturally, they're all
her own relatives but,
I guess I have to give her
credit for going all out
like she has.
♪ One day I... woke up,
a brand new day... ♪
Yeah... exactly
as I predicted...
♪ One day far beyond
the deep, blue sky, ♪
♪ you and I shall meet. ♪
♪ As a gentle breeze... ♪
Beautiful...
Wonderful...
♪ A snow-white feather
comes drifting along... ♪
♪ swaying in the air. ♪
♪ I love you, I need you,
and I want to hold you, ♪
♪ my love I am
standing beside you. ♪
Oh, Big Sis...!
Right, next event!
Voila!
There!
Ooh...! Ah...!
To the next event!
What are you doing getting
all friendly with it?!
Huh?
Why does this keep happening?!
Why, hello there!
Hey, Belldandy.
You put that hand down...
She really is perfect after all.
Hm?
I said Belldandy's perfect...
Now wouldn't you
agree with me, Kei?
She's gorgeous...
has a great figure...
she's a talented singer...
she's sincere, gentle-hearted,
and everyone loves her.
And to think my brother
actually has a woman like that
all to himself...
You lucky dog!
How'd you manage
that, huh, Kei?!
She's absolutely right.
I never really
thought about it...
but I really do have
this incredible goddess,
Belldandy, all to myself.
Belldandy?
Yes?
Today's entertainment has been
a big success thanks to you...
So how about you and
I have a little toast?
Sure! I'd be glad to!
No, Belldandy, wait!
Oh, take it easy, Kei!
Will you please let
go of me, Megumi?!
Sayoko is definitely
up to something!
So, you mean you
don't wanna see?
See what?
See what Belldandy's
gonna look like
after she gets a
little liq-uored-up?
WHAA-?!
Oh, Keiichi...
Wait, Belldandy!
Please don't do it!
You've gotta stop!
Cheers!
Ah...! That was very nice.
Then please have some more!
Thanks!
Belldandy, no!
Gin, rum, vodka, awamori...
I've got it all...
Now drink yourself into oblivion
in front of this whole crowd.
Make a fool of yourself.
Yes, just like you've
done to me so many times.
That one was very nice, too.
Just who the hell IS this girl?!
You little snake!
It's time for my last resort.
Spirytus, the world's
most potent liquor--
one-hundred
ninety-two proof,
ninety-six percent
alcohol by volume!
Even Belldandy will be
no match for this stuff!
Hey, watch where
you're falling, Sayoko!
Whoa! Sayoko, NO!
Ugh... I don't feel so good...
Are you all right?
Nothing went wrong at all?
Oh, no... I'm fine,
although I still don't know
too much about this
"liquor" stuff.
Oh, man... she can even
handle her liquor, too...
Here. I got her this
for her hangover.
I thought you guys had
better take it home with you
for in the morning... Bye!
Megumi...
Your little sister
always seems to be
looking out for you, isn't she?
She's just giving
me a hard time.
Well, here ya go...
It's some cola
for your hangover.
Then I thank you very much!
Although...
I guess you won't really need
it since you're not drunk...
No...
I have never tasted this kind
of drink before, besides...
Megumi got it just for me,
so I'm happy to drink it.
Okay, then?
Mm-hm.
But still, you already
drank all that liquor,
so don't push
yourself, all right?
I can't believe she's
never had cola before...
Ah!
Tasty?
Yes, this one is my
favorite of them all!
Yeah...? That's great...
Hey, Keiichi!
Uh, Hasegawa,
how trashed are you?
I am not a middle
school student!
A what?!
C'mon, I want you to
have a look... at these!
--GAAHHH!
--See, even I have boobs.
I'm just not very
tall, that's all!
I know I still have a
baby face, but check it out:
I DO have boobies...
Not only is she a crying drunk,
but she's all touchy feely...!
Huh? What's wrong?
--I think I get it now.
--Get what?
I think I better
just show you...
AAAAAAHHHH!
Huh...? Belldandy?
You poor thing!
You understand how
I feel, don't you?!
Could she be drunk...?
No way! On COLA?!
Oh, Miss Hasegawa,
you poor dear thing!
Is that how it works
with goddesses?
You really do understand...!
I am utterly miserable!
Aah...!
Let fortune smile on you.
I am so happy for you...
Miss Hasegawa.
Keiichi...! Look at me.
I've finally become
a real grown-up!
Hasegawa!
That is not what it
means to be a "grown-up!"
Did I just get hit in
the head with a sink?
Morisato!
What do I do now?
I guess Belldandy's cover
is finally gonna be blown!
--Good work, Hasegawa!
--Yeah, nice trick!
But no underclassman's
gonna out-do us!
You got it, Den!
They think it's part
of the entertainment.
I need to get
Belldandy out of here
while I still have a chance!
So what are we gonna do, Den?
Excuse me,
was there a young woman
standing here just a minute ago?
Yeah, there sure was,
but then she handed me
this bag of potato chips
and went outside.
WHAT?!
She did what?!
I've never heard of anyone
getting drunk off cola before,
but then I guess
it does sound like
something she'd do, doesn't it?
Well, in any case, I'm gonna
go try to find her right now!
Hey, Keiichi! Wait for me!
Keiichi!
Dammit...
I feel like I'm in a manga!
Meow, meow...
I see... Is that right?
Meow...
Oh, yes... Right!
You're very hungry, aren't you?
Let fortune smile on you.
Mew!
This has Belldandy
written all over it.
Hey! Knock it off, will ya?
I summon lightning!
Now you've done it! Skuld Bomb!
Aaack...! Oh, crap...!
What the heck's going on here?!
At long last I have returned!
The wounds I received
from the Lord of Terror
were worse than I
could've ever expected,
so it took quite
some time to recover.
But now I am...
fully rejuvenated!
My disgrace can only be cleansed
when I have defeated
you, Belldandy!
Let fortune smile on you.
Waaaaaahh!
I apologize, Mr. Telephone Pole.
You were stuck standing
there for such a long time...
Please relax and
get some rest now.
Belldandy, it IS you!
Mara, it's you!
Ah, that was your handiwork
just now, wasn't it...?
You sensed my presence and
launched a preemptive attack.
Exactly what I'd expect of a
First Class goddess like you!
However, I will be the
one who wins in the end!
Belldandy... I'll take you down!
Oh, Mara, you poor thing...!
So that is your
wish then, is it?
Don't call me a "poor thing!"
Let fortune smile on you.
Huh...?! What in the hell...
do you think you're doing?!
I was simply taken down,
exactly as you had wished.
Your happiness is
to be fulfilled
by my being taken down, correct?
Stop making fun of me!
I hate you sooo much Belldandy!
Oh, that Mara...
She was so overcome
with happiness,
it moved her to tears.
Waaah!
Look what you did to
my poor little Shiro!
I'm really sorry!
But I barely pulled on it!
Belldandy! Belldandy!
Don't tell me that
Belldandy's going around
spreading "happiness"
all over the place!
Eh...?!
Why on earth do
I keep having such
unbelievably
rotten luck today?
Huh?
Let fortune smile on you.
No, stop! Belldandy!
--What happened?!
--Hey, Mister...!
Huh?
Belldandy!
Mr. Keiichi, you poor thing!
Are you sure you're
felling all right?
I want to take away
your pain, Mr. Keiichi.
Here! It's the magician lady.
--She wants to talk to you.
--Magician lady?
So how's it going where you are?
Urd?
Well, it looks like you
managed to find her.
What's that...?
Belldandy is spreading
happiness all over the place?
Cut it out!
It's all right. No major
damage has been done yet.
The Law of Conservation
of Happiness dictates that
you will suffer misfortune
inversely proportional
to the good
fortune she bestows.
I get it now...
So that's why all those
things happened to me!
Essentially, a goddess's
job is to impart happiness.
Ahh! I'm, uh, pretty busy here,
so I'll leave Belldandy
in your hands! Ciao!
Wait, Urd, don't hang up!
OW...! Why's a stuffed
bear biting me?!
Please let go, Shiro!
Belldandy!
Ah... I can hear them...
I can hear the sorrowful
sighs of the people.
I must do something. I have to!
My heart yearns
for a soul mate...
I hear them...
This steep hill sure
is hard on me ...
I hear them.
Grr...!
I hear them!
Let fortune smile... on you all!
A plate of... sole...
So, I just got a... sole plate?
Now this is the life!
Woof, woof!
Huh? Ah?!
This sure is a heck of a
way to be granting wishes...
It looks like the
only question now
is whether I'll physically
be able to hold on
long enough to find
Belldandy... Although...
Oh, it's the dentures
I flushed down the toilet!
My VHS player works!
I can walk! It's a miracle!
Yeah... if I follow this trail,
I should be able to find her.
I can still hear
them out there...
I need to impart
even more happiness!
Belldandy!
Huh...?
Getting out for some fresh air
was definitely the right move...
It would certainly seem
that the goddess of fate
has not decided to
abandon me after all...
Oh, no...
I believe you are
confused, Mr. Aoshima.
I am not the goddess of fate.
I disagree! As far
as I am concerned,
you are the Goddess
of Fate, Herself!
I ask you now to grant
me your good fortune!
Huh? Did you say good fortune?
I certainly did!
Why would a respectable
person like myself
be treated in such a fashion?
I mean, can't you see that
my heart is in tatters?!
Oh, you poor thing!
Do you really mean that?
Of course...!
But isn't there anything I could
do that would ease your pain?
Jackpot!
Finally...!
How I've waited
to hear those words!
How I've waited for this moment,
when you become mine
in mind, body and soul!
Belldandy...!
I want to have YOU!
HUH?!
Essentially, a goddess's
job is to impart happiness.
C'mere, you!
That is the one thing
I cannot do for you.
Huh?
What are you talking about?!
You said you'd do ANYTHING!
Mm... You see...
Since I have already made
a promise to Mr. Keiichi...
Ah...
Not Keiichi again!
So everything you just
said to me was all a lie!
Oh, no...
Truly, it is my wish
to bring happiness
to all creatures here on Earth.
Then why won't you
be mine, Belldandy...?
Can't you see I am in
the very pit of despair?!
Well, Mr. Aoshima, it is because
I have an even bigger wish...
My wish is to always be
together with Mr. Keiichi.
And, most importantly, that
wish is one which we both share.
That wish is the greatest and
most important wish of all.
I will never betray this wish,
no matter what anyone
else may ask of me.
But any wish other than that
would be perfectly
fine, all right?
Don't give me that!
You think I'm gonna go
along with that crap...?!
You're gonna take responsibility
for what you said!
--Oh, Mr. Keiichi!
--I had good fortune there,
and then bad fortune
there and then...
I had good fortune there,
then more misfortune--
What the hell are you doing?!
Uh-huh... That means I
still have one round left!
C'mon!
Waaaaahh!
But why...?!
Because I've realized something.
Life's not perfect.
If it were, we wouldn't have
to run away from anything.
But at least we're holding
hands while we're running.
I'm afraid if I let go...
she'll vanish...
Even though I know all wishes
may not necessarily come true...
Someday...
I'll take this hand and...
I think we should
be all right now.
Mr. Keiichi?
Huh?
I would like you to
tell me if you have been
suffering any misfortune today.
No, not at all...
Well, not any more than usual.
But the real misfortune
is that sooner or later
I'll have to let go
of this hand of yours.
Let fortune smile on you.
Oh...!
Uh, Belldandy!
Hey, Belldandy?!
I guess it's no surprise,
considering how much
of her power she's used.
There we go...
Ahh!
Huh...? What'd you say...?
You can't let go of her hand?
Well, all things considered,
that's no big deal.
Check it out!
I'm a grown-up!
Hey look, you guys.
No way! Tomorrow morning?! Uh?!
Tomorrow morning, huh...
Well, I guess
that'll be all right.
Their fated meeting
came suddenly.
And it was only an instant
before they had fallen in love.
But there is one who aims
to come between them...
Next time, "Ah!
Well-Matched Vibes of Love."
What?! Is that what she's into?!