Ah-choo!
Ah...
It's starting to get
pretty cold, huh?
Yes, it certainly is.
These poor weak humans are so
susceptible to the elements.
In fact, he might
even catch a cold
wearing such light clothing.
You say you want to take
a few days off from class,
starting tomorrow?
Yes...
Well, with the grades
you get, I don't think
taking a few days off
will set you back too much.
Well, all right then.
Okay... time to get started...
Christmas time...
[chattering]
...a time when I, the
Queen of Nekomi Tech,
shine my brightest.
Miss... Mishima!
That's right.
They all want to
be chosen by me!
But why... isn't
that fulfilling...?
Deep down, I'm unsatisfied.
What in the world could a
woman of my means and status
possibly be lacking?
What's up, Sayoko?
Good morning, Keiichi...!
What the...
Hey, Kei! What's up?
Good morning.
Don't tell me Belldandy's
given you the cold shoulder.
Aw geez! Are you gonna
start giving me that, too?
Well, that is what everyone
on campus is thinking!
Hey, give me a break.
It's only been two days!
But you two are so close,
that it makes people talk.
So, you're still all
hot and steamy then?
Give it a rest, will ya?!
Ooooh! You're so scary!
I've got it!
Now I know
exactly what to do
to fill this emptiness
I've been feeling.
There is but one
man on this campus
whom I've been unable
to conquer...
Keiichi Morisato...
I now have my sights
squarely set on you...
and my heart will surely be
content once you are mine!
Honestly, Big Sis, when are
you gonna be done with that?
I'll be finished soon.
Aw... But all you've
been doing lately
is knitting that stupid thing!
I'm sorry, Skuld.
I'll tell you what.
When I'm finished, I'll make
you some ice cream, okay?
Belldandy... surely
you must realize
a goddess among
goddesses like you...
could make a hand-knitted
sweater in an instant
if she used her powers.
I call on you to dance,
my beloved yarn.
Entwine and mingle
together to become one!
Ta-dah! Uh-oh...
Who the heck would wear that?!
I'LL show ya how it's done!
This is the fully automatic
hand-knitting machine,
Amigo Zero-One!
With this little number, you'll
have your sweater lickety split!
"Fully automatic" would mean it
isn't HAND-knitted, you know...
Just shut up and watch!
Switch on!
All done!
What the heck is she doing?
Knitting is not just about
simply "making" something.
You knit so that
every single stitch
will give warmth to the
person who wears it.
There are all these
feelings and memories...
that go into a
person's knitting.
I suppose I'll never be able to
understand that kind of stuff.
But it sure does look... warm.
Why, thank you! Mm...
Hey... why are you keeping
this sweater a secret anyway?
Because...
that way it can be
more of a surprise
...for Mr. Keiichi.
Huh?
Is something wrong?
Well... it's just that
you've definitely become
much more like an ordinary human
since you came to
the surface world.
You think I've
become like a human?
Oh...!
I'm home!
Mr. Keiichi!
Welcome home!
So she's planned a surprise...
for our little Keiichi, has she?
Why does everything always
have to be so complicated?
Ha! So you got dumped
by Belldandy, didn't you?
Why would you say that?
Aren't you upset?!
Look, you've got it all wrong.
Is this seat taken?
Hm? Sayoko?
Sitting alone and bored, huh?
Looks like you're in the
same boat right now, huh?
Mm! It's not the same!
Anyway, it's getting pretty
close to Christmas, isn't it?
Wouldn't you like to
spend a wonderful evening
on the town with me, Keiichi...?
We could rent out a Five-star
hotel and have a gigantic party
or take luxury liner on
a cruise around Tokyo Bay.
It'd be a letdown to be alone
on Christmas Eve of all nights!
I'm flattered that you'd be so
concerned about me, Sayoko,
but uh... don't worry
about me. Really.
Ah...! What do you mean?
Well, Belldandy has been
with me for nearly a year now,
and she's gone to an awful
lot of trouble for me
on more than one occasion...
so I figure it's
only right to give her
some time to herself
for a change.
It sounds like you sure have
a lot of trust in her...
But I am curious
what she's doing
with all this "time to herself."
Now you don't suppose...
she's off doing something
like what we're doing.
I guess I never really
considered that possibility.
Ah...! I was only
joking, obviously!
Because if Belldandy really
were that kind of girl,
then I wouldn't have to go
through so much trouble to...
Uh...!
You actually do trust Belldandy
not to do anything like that,
don't you?
Hey, ya know something, Sayoko,
that's what I like about you.
Belldandy's always putting
everyone else's needs
before her own,
so I'm happy that she's finally
doing something for herself.
On top of that, it's
always a lot of fun for me
to try to imagine Belldandy
as I've never seen her before,
like doing whatever
it is she's doing now...
He's... boasting about her?
Keiichi of all people...?
That's why...
you don't have to worry, cause
it's really not that bad
for me to be on my own
for a little while.
Actually, things are probably
much tougher for you, Sayoko,
since you always have so many
people around you all the time,
and I'm sure you're
constantly having to take them
into consideration, right?
But I'm positive that Belldandy
and I are gonna be just fine.
Oh...! I haven't said
anything offensive, have I?!
Mm-mm...
Oh, it's almost time
for my lecture!
Huh?
I appreciate your concern.
I'll see you later.
Sayoko made me realize that
it's what's in a person's heart
that counts, ya know?
Hmph! Some "man."
You wouldn't have a chance of
drinking me under the table
in a million years.
Really...
These men truly are an utter
waste of my valuable time.
What a snooze!
Men are just way too dull!
How could a guy turn a girl down
after having her go so far?
Is that normal?!
Uh, hey... are you
listening to me or what?
Sheesh!
What's he mean "it's a
person's heart that counts?"
What the hell would
I know about that?
After all, no one's ever said
anything like that to me before.
Why...?
Why do the words and the
smile of a pathetic guy like him
have the power to
make a queen like me
feel like such a
piece of garbage?!
Keiichi, you damn stinkin' jerk!
What is that?
It looks like it's a person...
Sayoko?!
Ah... it's Keiichi!
Oh man, she is
totally plastered.
You're gonna catch a cold if
you sleep out here, Sayoko!
Keiichi!
Waaaahh!
Hey! I'm all over Keiichi...
Now hold on... Sayoko!
Hey, listen. You know what?
I never... told you this
before, but I really...
Huh?
Oh... this is bad...
NOOO!
Uh... How on earth
did I get here anyway?
Mm... Ah, my head
is killing me...
Guess I drank a little too much.
Hm...? Is this...
Keiichi's place?
Hm?
He never ceases to amaze me...
Don't worry, Mr. Keiichi.
This sweater shouldn't
take much longer to finish.
Oh, brother! So that's what
she's doing in there, huh?
But I don't understand
why she looks so happy
to be knitting a sweater.
I'm finished!
I've woven my feelings
into every single thread
of this sweater.
And I hope that it will keep
Mr. Keiichi nice and warm.
Mr. Keiichi.
Hey, Big Sis.
You were looking for some
wrapping paper, right?
Just look! I found
some that's perfect!
Oh, thank you very much!
I'll use it to wrap
Mr. Keiichi's sweater in.
Hey, come here a second!
Is something wrong?
Oh, what's her problem now?!
Geez! At your age you should be
able to zip up your own clothes
in the back,
for cryin' out loud!
There's nothing wrong...
I'm just touchy feely.
--Gasp!
--Hm?
It's gone! Vanished!
Mr. Keiichi's... sweater.
AAH! And she's gone, too!
But why...?
She's gonna pay for
stealing your sweater!
Well, we are not yet
certain that she did.
Come on...
it's not like that sweater
walked out of here by itself.
But, Urd...
There was only one
person near that sweater
when it disappeared...
And she vanished before we
even knew that she was gone.
She's right!
I can't think of anyone
else who could've done it!
Miss Sayoko is not a bad person.
But still!
You've gotta face the facts...
Ah...!
I have an idea!
The birds might
have seen something.
Tell me... what did you see?
You say a dog ran
away from here
with the package in his mouth?
Did the bird say why a dog
would've taken the sweater?
All he told the bird
was that the package had
a delicious smell about it.
A delicious smell, huh...?
Stop right there.
I get it now.
The dog was attracted to the
scent of the wrapping paper
and made off with the package.
That's right!
It's the dog's fault!
Sorry but... whose fault was it?
Sorry, Big Sis!
I'll be sure to give you
your full punishment later.
I've got to find it!
Belldandy!
It's only knitting.
I should be able to do it...
It's not like he'd be
happy about something...
with no feeling in it.
I wonder if he could ever
be happy about something
I knitted for him.
Ahh...!
N-No, stop!
Hand-knitting nowadays
is just plain silly!
That's right!
If I find their price,
anyone will wag their
tail like a dog for me!
Hello, there's something
I'd like you to make for me
on short notice.
No, don't worry about the cost.
Surely you're like most guys.
You are, aren't you, Keiichi?
Excuse me, I have a
question if you don't mind.
Have you seen a
package like this?
Meow...
Oh... Yes, I understand.
And I certainly do thank you.
Excuse me, Mr. Sunfish.
Have you seen a
package like this one?
Thanks...
Thanks anyway.
I thank you...
Keiichi.
Hey Sayoko...
Are you feeling better?
I am. Thanks to you.
That's good to hear.
Boy, sure was hard to
get that smell out though!
What does that mean?
Oh, never mind.
I see...
It looks like I was a huge
burden on you yesterday, huh?
Oh hey, don't worry about it!
And besides, Belldandy was
the one who took care of you.
Oh... I really don't recall...
How about I repay you by
treating you to a banquet
of French Court cuisine
aboard a luxury liner?
Actually, I can't
have dinner with you.
Why not?
So you're saying that you
don't want to eat with me?
It's just that
I'm sure Belldandy
already has something
waiting for me.
Hey, you should eat
with us sometime!
She's a great cook!
You just... keep going
on about her...
All right then, could we do
something besides dinner?
Well... I guess so.
Let's go then.
Come on, already!
All this searching
and still nothing...
But, I will not
give up my quest!
Because that sweater...
contains all of
my deepest feelings.
Please accept this as
a token of my gratitude.
I never would have
guessed that retro car shop
was run by the
Mishima conglomerate.
Thanks to you, I got to see
their prized collection
of rare model cars.
It's my father's
hobby, you know.
That's where I got those
model cars from that time.
Yeah, that was a pretty
terrible thing you did
to torture me back then.
Well, my father really chewed me
out because of that incident,
so cut me a little
slack, will ya?
It's fun just to walk along
with him like this...
And it... gives me this
strange kind of feeling.
Hey, Keiichi...
How do you think
the two of us look
to other people right now?
Hmm. Good question...
Probably like a queen
and her servant, I guess.
Hey... I was only joking around!
Seriously though, I guess we
look like a couple of friends.
You think so?
Y'know. A lot has
happened between us,
but now I feel like we can
just be normal with each other.
And a lot of that is due to
the fact that I met Belldandy.
Otherwise, I'd be the same,
old guy I used to be...
and I probably wouldn't
even be able to
walk around with you like this.
What's with this guy anyway...?
He doesn't have the slightest
clue as to how women feel.
Hey, Keiichi...
What's up?
I'd be honored if
you'd accept this gift...
It's a Christmas
present from me to you.
I see...
But isn't it a waste
to give this to me?
But why? It's a high
quality cashmere sweater!
You'd never be able
to afford one of these
with the part-time
wages you make!
But I... still can't accept it.
I don't understand.
What's the big deal anyway?
It's just that...
I feel like it's what's in a
person's heart that counts.
So, are you saying my
heart doesn't make the cut?!
Look, it's not like that.
It's just that your heart is
closed off to others, Sayoko.
I don't know if it's
because I'm around Belldandy
so much of the time...
but I think I can sense
those things about people now.
So I think you ought to
give that Christmas present
to someone who you can really
express your feelings to.
Does that make sense?
I see...
Fine! I give up then!
Honestly, I just can't hang
around with you men at all!
What morons...
Sayoko...
Wha...?
I found that next to the road...
I was thinking
I'd just toss it...
but I'm giving it to you!
And if you tell me you
won't take this either,
I'll beat some sense into you!
But, isn't this...
Just take it...
and wear it home.
You'll understand later.
I'm sure... that she's
still looking for it...
Hurry up and go on home!
Okay...
Miss Sayoko!
I certainly do hope that you're
feeling better this evening.
I was so worried about you.
I guess you've been searching
this whole time, huh?
Well... never mind...
Your feelings are getting
across to him right about now.
Are you talking
about the sweater?
So, I take it
you know about it?
Yeah... After all,
I'm the one who stole it from
your house to begin with.
To tell you the truth. I wanted
to throw the damn thing out.
But I...
just couldn't do it.
The reason is that...
you are simply not
that kind of person.
Oh, can it, will ya...?!
Don't hand me that crap, okay?!
I don't want to hear it.
Okay...
--Belldandy?
--Yes?
I am the heiress Sayoko Mishima.
And I'm... Queen of Nekomi Tech.
So tell me...
who in the hell are you?
I am a Goddess First Class,
Second Category,
Unlimited License.
I am Belldandy.
Oh...
Well then... I suppose
I should just tell you...
I hate your guts.
Well even so... I shall
still love you, Miss Sayoko.
And now, if you'll excuse me...
What a liar...
You're no goddess,
knitting a sweater
for Keiichi like you did...
I don't believe it.
You're just an ordinary girl.
Hello everyone, I'm home.
Oh, look! It's Big Sis!
Hey, c'mon, Keiichi! Hurry up!
Welcome home, Belldandy.
It's good to have you back.
Ah! My feelings...
They came across to you!
They did!
I'm so glad!
Your feelings came
across all right...
Thanks for everything,
Belldandy.
And you know what...
This sweater is nice and warm.
It's all right.
Because I am the
Queen, after all.
Keiichi... if you think that
I've given up on you,
then you are sorely mistaken.
One of these days,
I'll get even with you...
And I'll make you
regret humiliating me
like you did today.
He tries so hard to return the
feelings of his goddess.
The goddess believes in him,
and continues waiting all alone
for him to come home.
Next time, "Ah! I Offer These
Feelings on Christmas Eve."
It's what's in a person's heart
that matters most... isn't it?