Welcome! And how can I help you?
Would you like me to warm up
this boxed lunch for you?
Uh yeah, sure. That'd be great.
And I'd like a sweet
roll, too, please.
I'm terribly sorry...
but they're still in the
oven and not ready yet.
But, if you'd like one of
our new soy flour rolls,
we've got plenty!
All right, I'll
try one of those.
Oh, great! Let me get you one!
Delivery!
Hey, good to see you!
I can't believe how many
magazines come out on Mondays...
It's a pain because
I gotta restock
all the boxed lunches then too!
Then I got a guy who orders a
sweet roll at a time like this.
What the hell is
he thinking anyway?
Oh, well, no point
grumbling about it...
This is after all just
a necessity for survival.
--Um, excuse me...
--Huh?
Is... my boxed lunch ready yet?
And if it isn't too
much trouble, Miss,
I'm still waiting for
that soy flour roll, too...
--Aaack!
--Aaaahh!
Hey! You forgot to sign this!
You need you to sign
the receipt, Mara!
What a bunch of IDIOTS!
I am the Lady Mara, Demon
First Class, Unlimited License!
Why's the Office of Demonic
Affair's Number One employee...
doing menial labor at a stupid
convenience store...?!
Whilst only making
ten bucks an hour?!
And why is there a
twenty percent increase
for working the midnight
to six A.M. shift?!
Well, that is a whole dollar
and seventy cent increase
from the eight-fifty
an hour you started at.
Well, that's true. But you see,
the owner of the store told
me that I've been showing
a lot of potential
for advancement.
Could we expect any less from
the Office of Demonic Affair's
Number One employee?!
Aw, you flatter me.
Hey, and get this:
the owner said that
he could probably even let me
handle managing the place!
Congratulations on your
promotion to manager! Yay!
Hurray!
And please keep on bringing us
these delicious boxed lunches!
You just leave it to me...!
Hey! Hold on!
I was asking you how I ended up
like this in the first place!
Well, forgive me for saying
so, but it's because
you screwed up so many of
your missions, remember?
What did you say?!
...because our lousy
research and development!
That's exactly right!
And since you've learned
from your mistakes,
I want you to get to work
on your next invention!
With all due respect,
Lady Mara...
that's going to be
quite difficult
with the equipment we have here.
I think it may be best if
we return to the demon realm.
You imbecile...!
If I were to go back now,
I'd be a laughing stock!
And besides, the ruler of
demonkind wouldn't tolerate it!
Mm... You must mean
Lady Hild. Am I right?
Don't say that name out loud!
Just hearing it gives
me the total creeps!
Oh, man! Is she ever
scary or what?!
Enjoying the part-time job?
Oh, you bet! I'm totally
set from now on!
With hard work and dedication,
I could become the
manager in no time.
I'd just love to have
one of those boxed lunches
that you've heated
up for me, Mara!
LA... LADY HILD?!
Please accept my
humblest apologies!
This convenience store boxed
lunch isn't all that bad really.
I can't really say I'm all that
surprised you didn't notice me,
even though I've been
sitting right next to you
this whole time.
But, M'lady...
Oh, what's this...?
You see, I split off one
thousandth of myself
just before I went back.
Since I do have things I still
needed to take care of here.
Oh, well, that certainly
is interesting.
So, how's the expansion of
our shares coming along, Mara?
I sincerely hope you're
not going to tell me
you haven't made any
progress, now are you?
Um, well... Uh...
Are you sure it's all right
to let those goddesses
do whatever they please?
No, ma'am! Of course not!
First Class Demon,
Unlimited License, Mara...
I'd say I know your power better
than anyone, don't you agree?
Oh, yes, Lady Hild!
So if you really put
your mind to it,
you could beat those
goddesses, couldn't you?
Why yes, of course
I could, Lady Hild!
Then I believe it's about time
you showed those high
and mighty goddesses
why they should
fear you... Right?
YES, MA'AM!
I'm on it. I'll go
do it right now!
--Belldandy?
--Hm?
Have you seen my blue
jacket around anywhere?
Oh, yes.
I believe I washed it
for you yesterday.
Just a minute...
I'll go get it for you.
Oh, it's all right.
Don't worry about it.
I can just go get it myself!
--Darn right!
--Huh?
If you think you can make
Big Sis go fetch YOUR laundry...
So you plan to attack
them head-on... eh?
Right! When you really
think about it,
I am one of the
most feared demons
in all of the demon realm.
When I get serious,
a mere goddess or two
won't stand a chance
of getting in my way.
Don't worry! Just leave
everything to me, Lady Hild!
Oh...? Well, whatever you say.
I'll just leave it to you then.
Hm! Just you watch,
you stinkin' goddesses.
Let's go, Octopus, Senbei!
Chu-chu!
You called, Milady.
And voila! Here I am.
SHAKKIN!
Let's do it!
Leave it all to Senbei, Milady.
You have nothing to fear!
And now it's showtime!
Huh...?!
Huh?!
It's been a while, so I totally
forgot about that thing...
Well, I'll be damned if
I'm gonna let a little thing
like that slow down
my rise to glory!
I say, this Japanese
wasabi is just sublime!
My word! What on earth
is this bizarre thing?!
Oh, no! My octopus!
Blimey, it's an OCTOPUS!
The so-called "devil fish"!
Hey! Give it back, you guys!
That octopus belongs to me!
--Oh, my God!
--Huh?
Surely its owner is the
incarnation of Death herself!
--C'mon!
--Let's jam, Pete!
Okay, Roger! You got it!
Oh, my... what beautiful music!
What'd they have to
do that for? Damn it!
If this is how it's gonna be,
then I guess Senbei's all
I've got left to rely on!
Senbei!
Shakkin!
Just leave everything
to me, my dear Mara,
and I'll make it look as easy
as taking candy from a baby!
I'm counting on you, Senbei!
Our target is right there.
Have no fear! She's no match
for my powers of bad luck...!
--Shakkin!
--OW!
Oh dear, dear, dear!
That's my bad!
You idiot! I told you,
she's the target, not me!
I am fully aware
of that, Milady!
Just a case of bad timing...
Ah - Shakkin!
Ahh!
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
You see, I have a chronic
case of hayfever...
What the hell are
you talking about?!
It's just a common
pollen-induced allergy.
You gotta tell me about
these things first!
Shakkin! Shakkin! Shakkin!
You had me worried there.
What is with you? Those
sneezes are totally faked!
When people sneeze, they
go "Ah-choo". "AH-CHOO!"
Why the hell do you
even say "shakkin"?!
That's the Japanese
word for "debt."
Do you have a demonic bank loan?
Were you affected by
the economic collapse?!
And why do you talk like
those funny rocker guys?!
I'll bet you're in cahoots
with them, aren't you?
Huh... I-I forgot about him.
YAAAAAH!
Oh, dear...
Banpei certainly seems to
have a lot of energy today!
I guess Mara really is
hopeless, isn't she...?
She's certainly not
gonna get anywhere
if she keeps up like this.
Guess I have no choice.
I don't know how much
more of this I can take.
The situation seems to be
going from bad to worse.
Now what do I do?
Huh?
Hey! This is the
Heretical Pot...!
What the heck is
it doing out here?
Well, who cares
how it got here...
This is the opportunity
I've been waiting for!
I gotta strike while
the iron's hot!
--All right, I'm heading out.
--Huh?
What time do you think
you'll you be back?
Oh, I really don't think
I'll be out that late...
Hyaah!
Mara?!
Say your prayers,
Belldandy! Take THIS!
Ah...! Keiichi!
--Are you all right?
--You fool!
That was exactly what
I expected you would do!
Huh?
Ah!
I'm gonna split your
personality in two!
Just like I did
with your sister Urd!
Okay... Let's just see
where this gets her...
Belldandy!
Well, it seems as though
nothing has happened.
What?
WHAT THE HELL WENT WRONG?!
That is the Heretical Pot.
I'm sure of it!
There's no way you
shouldn't have been split!
What the heck's going on here?!
--You're so dense.
--Huh?
The Heretical Pot worked on me
because I'm half-goddess,
half-demon,
but there's no point using it
on someone like Belldandy.
Huh? What's that
supposed to mean?
Cause she doesn't even have a
split personality to begin with.
AAAAAAHHHH!
Aw... too bad for poor Mara.
Hey, listen...
I've been meaning to tell
you this for a while...
but you have
absolutely NO talent.
As a demon, you simply
have no talent whatsoever.
Surely, you must
realize that deep down.
Why don't you just give up and
go back to the demon realm?
You know, there's a line when
it comes to being offensive,
and you just crossed it!
You might not know by looking,
but I'm a Demon First Class,
Unlimited License.
I have exceptional skills,
my subordinates admire me,
and I'm gonna be manager at the
convenience store in no time!
I make over ten dollars an hour!
So telling me that I've got
no talent is just plain...
It's so very... just so very...
C'mon now, don't cry.
Oh, Mara! Well it certainly
sounds like things are going
very well with the
part-time job I got you.
Yeah. Thanks, Belldandy,
you were a real lifesaver!
We should have a celebration
in honor of your
promotion to manager.
Huh?
We'll have a nice
big hot pot tonight,
and it'll be tastier
if we all eat together.
Oh, Belldandy!
Belldandy may not have more
than one personality to split,
but I suspect that every goddess
has a hint or two of evil
somewhere deep down
inside of them.
Oh, well. I'm just glad I
decided to put her to the test.
Since she is the one goddess
that resembles him most of all.
This could prove to
be very entertaining...
So you see, there's
no need to cry.
We'll all enjoy a wonderful
celebration tonight.
Wow, I am STUFFED!
That Belldandy
is something else!
She sure can cook like
a First Class Goddess!
And it's a nice change from
eating those boxed lunches
all the time!
Man, those goddesses really are
a nicer bunch than I thought.
Tellin' me I can come back
over again whenever I like!
Welcome back!
La... La... Lady Hild! What are
you doing to my subordinates?
It's unfair for you
to be the only one
to have a hot pot tonight.
--So I'm making my own.
--NOOOOO!
I beg your forgiveness!
I'll never fail you
like this again!
Now don't get yourself
all worked up.
If you're as satisfied as you
seem, then I should be, too.
No, of course I'm not
satisfied, Milady!
But I thought you said you're
quite full at the moment?
Uh, well I, um...
Well, unfortunately,
I happen to be starving!
Lady Hild! Please give
me another chance!
I have a secret weapon that
I've been saving until now
and I humbly request your
permission to use it!
Oh, really?
Yes, really!
Look for yourself!
I've got it right here!
This is the ultimate
anti-goddess weapon:
the Devilish Divinity Vacuum!
Those goddesses are
the biggest threat to us
increasing our share, and with
this we can seal them all away!
All right. Try it out.
Huh?
I said give it a try.
AH... YES MA'AM!
Hm...
Just do it already!
Oh my!
Please, Lady Hild, get me out!
And just how might I do that?
Pour hot water over the lamp,
and rub it three times!
Not BOILING water!
Aw... fine.
Unfortunately, Mara,
there's one glaring flaw
in this plan of yours.
What...?! But you saw
that it sucked me in!
And who do you think is
going to put their lips
--to something like this?
--Huh?!
Oh, very well... If I must...
I guess I'll just have
to give you an idea.
You mean it, Lady Hild?!
One catch.
Yes?!
Get me some oden stew from
your convenience store.
I've wanted to try it for a
while now, Store Manager.
Aw, shucks!
--Don't laugh.
--Yes, ma'am.
Gimme a six...! Come on,
just gimme a six already!
Oh, boy... I don't know
what you're talking about.
Now hurry up and
play your next card.
Pass...
You can only pass
three times, remember?
I hate you, Urd!
Wait, Skuld!
She can be so
immature sometimes.
It's probably good we stopped.
I have some shopping that
I've been meaning to do today.
Can you get me the latest
issue of TV Afternoon?
All right!
Urd is such a big dummy!
I just don't believe this!
I'll never forgive her!
As long as she's around,
I won't be able to find
a moment's happiness
as long as I live!
This is all just
so unfair...! Huh?
Wow! It's SO cute!
I'll bet that Big Sis went
out and got this for me
to cheer me up and
make me feel better.
Oh, thank you so much, Big Sis.
Okay, I'm heading out.
See ya later.
Hey, Skuld...
Sorry about earlier.
I promise that next time
we'll play Monopoly,
since you're so
good at that game.
So come on out, okay? Huh?!
No way! She's just a character.
She couldn't really exist.
I... I mean... Ah...
It can't be,
there's no way!
It must be some
kind of a trap...!
Get a hold of yourself, Urd!
No doubt this is Mara's doing!
Or if not, then maybe
she is behind this!
Aww...
No, I mustn't.
I mustn't...
Your plan is working
perfectly, Lady Hild!
What can I say...?
People just can't
help themselves
when they're faced with the
thing that they happen to find
the most cute.
But I never would've expected
Urd of all people
to fall for it!
You just don't get it
at all, do you, Mara?
Huh?
Love may in fact be
the greatest weapon,
but then it can also be
one's greatest weakness...
Especially if that
love runs quite deep.
--'Scuse the interruption!
--Huh?
You here, Morisato?
Well, we're comin' in anyway...
AH!
This... this is...
...an ever elusive
Messerschmitt engine?
Morisato has some
nerve hiding...
Damn. Not the catch
we were looking for.
Patience, Mara. All in due time.
Uh, hello? Skuld, are you home?
Uh...!
I don't know... This is
starting to feel really wrong.
Look, it comes
with the territory.
You're supposed to
be a demon, remember?
--Hello!
--Huh?!
Hey, Kei! Are you
around or what?
Hey, what's this...?! Ah!
What a cute little boy!
What a cute scooter!
What a cute little kitty!
Damn it! What the hell is
talking Belldandy so long
to get back anyway?!
Well, she's certainly
been quite lucky so far.
Getting back so late
today of all days...
But then...
I'm back!
Man, I sure am hungry!
Hey, Belldandy...?
Huh?!
Chihiro, is that you?
Huh? Oh... don't
interrupt us right now.
B-But, Chihiro, wait! That's...
Mm... Ah!
She... disappeared!
Ah!
This is too weird. Belldandy
would never act like this.
And besides, what just
happened to Chihiro?
What did Chihiro
do to Belldandy?
And what the heck...
am I... doing?
I can't... do this.
Will you just kiss her and
get it over with already?
This guy is getting
on my nerves...
Well, if that's how
he's gonna be...!
It's no use, I can't
resist her! But... But!
But I...!
Get on with it already!
I don't think I've ever seen
such a wishy-washy,
indecisive little worm!
But, Lady Hild,
doesn't what we did
count as blatant use of force?
Mara, do you happen to know
what we say in times like this?
Yes! The ends justify the means!
Right!
I'm home everyone!
Uh!
Quick! Hide!
Urd? I brought you that issue
of TV Afternoon that you wanted.
Urd?
What's this?
Ah!
Ah...! Yes!
Ah...
It's so cute!
Here we go, at last!
YES!
What the...
Hey! What gives?!
I'll bet this is
some kind of antique
that Urd must of
bought recently.
But since it looks so dirty...
I think I'll just have to
clean it up for her, won't I?
It seems that it appears as just
an ordinary lamp to Belldandy.
I think the bigger concern here
is what she might try
to do with that thing.
I have a very bad
feeling about this, Mara.
That's hot water.
Yeah, it is...
Huh?!
I'm gonna get you all
cleaned up now, all right?
AAAH!
Aaaah...!
So cute! So cute! So cute!
Belldandy? Ah, yeah.
You're so cute!
Excuse me! But what are
you all doing here?!
What do you think
could've happened, Milady?
I'm guessing we managed to
overload that stupid lamp
with too many people.
What do you mean "overload"?!
Mara, where are you going?
Well, usually when there's
an overload of some sort,
it means that some kind of
explosion is going to follow!
--Mara!
--Yes?!
Why didn't you tell
me that earlier?
Oh, cool breeze,
I bid you to come forth
with your healing winds
and cure this
raging, furious soul!
Stop hitting me with those
nine-hit combos, you idiot!
Don't lie to me, you guys
are enjoying this. I know it!
--AAACK!
--I did it! Go! Get her!
You passed the test,
Belldandy.
It's so cute!
You were able to see
through to its true form
without being deceived.
Your kindness allowed
you to give yourself
so generously to it.
And your heart managed to
remain calm and tranquil
throughout it all.
This looks delicious.
Thanks, Belldandy!
It's always a pleasure
to cook for you.
Hey, Big Sis...
Those are all techniques
for showing love.
Mara might like to come over
tonight, so I made some...
But you know, Belldandy,
love can be the
greatest weapon...
it can, however, also be
the greatest weakness.
You'll understand soon enough.
This is great!
I gotta tell ya,
this is hands-down one of
the best meals I've ever had!
You say that about
everything she cooks!
Hey, that's not
true at all, Skuld!
Then give me a detailed
explanation of exactly what...
You're kidding, right?
I've summoned the
ultimate warrior
from the depths of
the demon realm!
Their goal is to
get between these two
and force her to
return to Heaven!
Next time, "Ah! The Love of
a Goddess Saves a Ninja."
Would you give this up already?
Oh boy...