Kei-i-chi...
Mm. Mm...
Oh, Keiichi...
Mm...
Wh-What is it?
Hello there, Keiichi.
Good morning.
W-What's going on?!
Isn't this to your liking?
Jeez! Do you have to be so noisy
this early in the morning?!
Belldandy doesn't ever do this
kind of thing for you, does she?
No! She doesn't! And I
don't want her to either!
Stop being so darn stubborn...
Make the right wish, and you
could have this all the time.
Oh, dear.
YOU'RE SO GROSS!
Uh?
Perhaps that was a little
over-stimulating for a child.
You know, if you keep
playing with toys like that,
you won't ever be able
to grant wishes...
You'll always be
completely useless.
These are not toys!
And I am not useless either!
Looks like we'll have to
continue this later...
as we've been so
rudely interrupted.
Grr... I can SO
do it, you big perv!
That's right. I am able
to grant people's wishes!
It's time to leave.
Huh?
So, you were up to
something again...
I believe I already told you
that it would be no use.
I am merely trying to
fulfill my obligation
as a First Class goddess.
Not that I'd expect a
Second Class goddess
like yourself to understand.
Now, if you'll please
excuse me, Urd.
As a First Class goddess,
I don't have the time to
simply lounge the day away
like someone of
the lower classes.
Are you trying to pick
a fight with me...?
That's fine...
cause I'm up for it.
Peorth!
Hm?
What is it this time?
Right! Let's begin.
We're having a contest to see
who the most useful goddess is!
Mm-hm...
It'll just be a little game...
not like a contract...
If we did it for real,
I'd be suspended for
violating regulations again.
Well, all the same,
the thing is--
You'll be the judge,
Keiichi. Just say yes.
Now, hold on...
As ridiculous as
this whole thing is,
I suppose I have no choice
but to accept the challenge.
I... don't exactly see
the point of this...
What's that...?! Go ahead
and make your wish!
You... don't listen...
All of you, stop it.
Will you please just
leave Keiichi alone?
Give me a break.
If you're so afraid that I'm
going to take him away from you,
then why don't you just
take part in this little
contest, too, Belldandy?
What?
Oh... how silly of me!
If you had the ability,
you would have already
granted Keiichi's wish
by now, wouldn't you?
But... I only... Uh...
Um, I need to get going to the
university right now, ladies,
so can we continue with this...
later, when I get back home?
WHAT?!
My teleportation spell will...
My transport gun will...
My dimensional
slide spell will...
TAKE YOU!
Aaaghhh!
Nothing beats a First Class
goddess' technique.
Quite charming if
I do say so myself...
My devices are the best
in the whole world!
Uh...?
The battle will be
decided on the campus!
Naturally!
You're both going down!
Oh, no...!
Keiichi's going to be...
It's no use following us.
If you come along,
you're only going to find...
that you're incapable
of granting his wish.
That isn't true! I...
You may mean to help Keiichi...
but I have to wonder if you
only cause him more trouble.
I'm right on the mark, aren't I?
Ever since that incident
between us so long ago,
what I have most hated
about you is your hypocrisy.
But, Peorth!
Just stay here and keep being
all wrapped up in yourself.
Then I will prove once and
for all that I am the one
who will grant Keiichi's
deepest heartfelt wish...
and not you.
Oh!
Keiichi...! That's not...
Not what?
Tamiya and the others broke
that bronze statue, and...
Whoooaaa!
Keiichi!
As I was trying to tell you,
they repaired it
with some wood glue,
but it's not really able to
support a person's weight,
so you shouldn't, uh...
--Guess I'm too late, huh?
--Ah-choo!
Ah-choo!
Oh, man! A cold bath sure does
get to you this time of year...
Hey, are you gonna
be all right?!
I'll go get you something
nice and warm to drink!
So cold, brr...
Sweater, come here!
Thermal Coating cartridge
is locked 'n loaded!
Anti-extreme-cold program,
"Summer Mode"!
Aaahhh!
Arrghhh!
Hey...! Wait...!
What's going on?!
What the hell?!
Ahh...! I... can't move!
Agh... It's so hot... Ugh...
Hmph! Well, I'm positive
my spell was perfect...
Just shows how Second Class
goddesses don't follow through.
What was that?!
You got a problem?!
Grrr!
What the heck is
going on here...?
Geez... I'm not sure
I even want to know.
I wonder why Belldandy
hasn't shown up yet...
I hope she's not still upset
about this whole
Peorth situation.
But how am I ever going to be
able to put her mind at ease
about this whole mess?
--K-Keiichi!
--Huh?
I brought you something warm!
Oh, thanks, Haseg--
Uh... Ah! AAAHH!
Uh. Uh...
Belldandy! I swear
I didn't see anything!
I might have known that's
the kind of thing he'd like.
How perverted...!
But I'll still win!
The object of men's desires is
the mystery of the female form.
Come then, let us
give him an eyeful!
GO!
What the heck?!
Keiichi!
Hasegawa!
Huh...? What's... happening?!
Someone help me!
I'm turning into the wind!
AAAHHH!
Becoming the wind...
Truly every man's fantasy...
That's not the issue here!
What on earth is going
to happen to him now?!
Wind magic never was in
my realm of specialty!
Then would you mind not using
magic outside that realm?
What has most likely happened
is that our spells have
interfered with each other
and, instead of
summoning the wind,
we have transformed Keiichi
into the wind itself.
So what will happen now?
Keiichi will fully
become one with the wind,
and never return to
his original form...
But in return, he can flip up
as many skirts as he likes.
AAAHH!
But, Urd...!
Hey... I'm just kidding!
Peorth, would you mind
canceling the spell?
I'm already on it. But still...
I don't know if even
I will be able to solve
this complicated formula...
Uh... I'm disappearing!
Keiichi!
Whoa...!
It's no good! I won't be
able to do it in time!
Keiichi!
Huh?
Ah...
--Belldandy!
--Careful, Big Sis!
It's all right...
I'm here for you now.
So come to me, Keiichi!
Come to me!
I'm sorry I took so long.
What did Big Sis do just now?
She managed to reassemble
Keiichi's particles
out of that
enormous whirlwind...
Even though she is an
expert with wind spells...
that was still quite impressive.
I can't believe
what she just did!
I can't believe she's capable
of such immense power...
I knew you wouldn't
get it, seeing as how
you only knew Belldandy
when she was up in Heaven.
And just what does that mean?
Well... I guess you'll just
have to face the facts.
What are you talking about?!
All right, all right, I lose!
C'mon Skuld...
We're going home.
Ow, ow, ow, ow! Big sis!
Uh... Um, Belldandy?
Oh, Keiichi!
I'm so sorry about...
what my sisters did.
I couldn't...
get them to stop...
Hey, you don't need
to apologize for that.
But I...
Thanks so much
for coming, Belldandy.
It really means a lot to me.
Keiichi!
You're always doing
so much for me...
Don't you ever feel like I don't
do enough for you in return?
Not at all!
Just the fact that you want
me here makes me happy enough,
and it gives me the
strength to do anything.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
I don't get it at all...
What the heck IS it
with those two anyway?
But you know, it's
because he's like that,
that Belldandy puts
so much faith in him.
Well, in that case,
it's quite simple.
All I need to do
is make Keiichi's heart
belong to me and only me.
Yes, no matter what it takes...
I'm back.
Welcome home!
Uh...?
I'm sorry...
I forgot. You were gone as well.
Huh? I meant to say...
Welcome back to you?
Ah...! Yes!
I'm back, too.
What? What the heck was that?
What is with the insanely
sticky-sweet atmosphere?
Is Keiichi really
satisfied with this
elementary-school-level
lovey-dovey nonsense?!
NO...! That simply
cannot be the case!
After all, I confirmed
earlier that he does indeed
experience the normal desires.
As I suspected,
it looks as though
I'll need to become even
more aggressive with him.
"Giant X" enlargement potion,
"P-One-Zero" underwater
breathing potion.
As usual, nothing
but worthless junk...
But where did she put
the one that I need?
Ah...! Here it is!
"Seeds of love"!
But this is a vulgar drug,
which will make its user
fall in love with
anyone at random.
I shall improve upon this
concoction and make it fabulous!
I shall call it "Drop of Love."
Once taken, this elegant drug,
will make its user
fall in love with only me.
♪ Cleaning, sweeping, cleaning,
sweeping, so much fun indeed! ♪
Oh, my! Doesn't that
seem just blissful!
Yes, Peorth?
So have you made any progress
in granting Keiichi's wish yet?
Well, I...
You make me ashamed to be to
be a fellow First Class Goddess.
What in Heaven's name have
you actually done for him
as a goddess?
A First Class
goddess is so named
because she can
grant all wishes.
That... is our
primary obligation.
You are therefore
neglecting your obligation!
Neglect? That's wrong. Ah...
I don't...
Spare me the excuses.
You see, I am quite
different from you.
I want to grant the
innermost wishes of his heart.
Obviously you don't.
I can't believe I'm sweating
so much in the winter...
Here.
Hm...? Okay...
thanks, I appre--
It's my pleasure, Keiichi.
--Uh...
--Uh?
Eh...
Oh, no! You must suspect me of
putting something in your drink!
How horrible!
That's what you were
thinking, isn't it, Keiichi?!
All right, all right,
I'll drink it!
Oh...? Really...?
Well, there definitely
wasn't anything in it.
Until now anyway...
When you open your eyes...
the only thing that you're going
to see, Keiichi, will be me.
Hang on...
What's he doing there?
Is something wrong?
Oh, no, Keiichi's just
taking a little break.
C'mon, let's go over that way
so as not to disturb
him, all right?
Hey, Peorth, hold on!
I hope I can grant every
single one of Keiichi's wishes.
Not because of my obligations
as a First Class goddess,
but because that's
what I want in my heart.
But...
Hello in there...!
I know that I'm a little late,
but I wanted to come
see the pictures!
And he's fast asleep.
You'll catch cold if you
go falling asleep out here!
Mm...? Megumi...
Uh-huh... Huh?!
Ah...?
I love you... so much.
I love you...
Hey, what's gotten into
you all of a sudden?
Oh, I get it! You're talking
about sisterly love, right?
No, not like that.
You see, I've finally noticed
your manly charms, Kei.
We can no longer be...
just "brother" and
"sister," understand?
NO! Let's keep being
just brother and sister!
Ah! B-But, Kei!
Are you telling me you don't
care about my feelings?!
There's nothing I
can do about them!
Come on, Kei!
Man...! What the heck
is going on with her?!
Geez, Keiichi!
Keep it down, will ya?!
I can't even hear the TV!
I'm sorry. You see,
Megumi's acting a little...
--Keiichi...
--Huh?
I love you.
What?
That boring haggard face...
and those dull clothes
that always look the same...
You're just so dreamy...
Uh... calm down, okay?
I love you, Kei!
What the heck's going on here?!
Oh, Keiichi?
The effect of the potion should
be kicking in right about now.
So come to me and tell me
your heart's greatest desire!
Ah...
Oh...! Keiichi!
It was you after all.
Oh... Keiichi!
Oh, Kei... I can't take it!
Your wish is my command,
Keiichi, and I mean every wish!
Somebody! Help me!
Hm...
No matter how many times I count
them, there's still one missing.
Somebody DO something!
Keiichi?
I might've known.
What the heck are you doing?!
Urd, is that you?
Please help me!
K-Keiichi?
AGH!
That was way too close...
Keiichi! I need you to
turn your head the other way.
Huh?
It would appear that Peorth
must've made you
swallow a Seed of Love.
Seed of Love? You mean...
This one was a little
different, though.
It seems she altered a Seed
of Love and turned it into
a drug of sheer temptation
that makes anyone who
looks at you your captive.
Why would she make
something like that?!
She probably just blew it.
Not just any yo-yo can waltz
in and use those potions.
I can see that.
I'll make you an antidote,
so just wait there.
Okay! I'm counting on you!
I really don't want Belldandy
to end up like this too...!
Huh?!
Whatever you do...
don't look at me right now!
Uh!
Uh...
I love you!
This is just great.
You've got a lot of
nerve barging in here!
Well, you're not taking
my Kei away from me!
Hmph! All's fair in
love and war, girls.
You said it!
And that is why I am not
going to hold anything back.
Hm?!
Keiichi?
Seriously... Belldandy,
don't look at me!
The Seed of Love that Peorth
made will only mess you up, too!
Keiichi!
Is it really so painful for
you to turn... and face me?
What?! What do you mean?
I still want to be here,
even if it is!
I still want to be
with you by your side!
Right now, I am unable
to grant the wish
Peorth says you have
deep within your heart.
The truth is I want to make
all of your wishes come true!
Not out of any obligation
as a First Class goddess,
but because I want to grant
them of my own free will!
But... would you still accept
me... even like I am...?
Would you... Keiichi?
Even if being with me...
would lead to something even
more difficult later on...
Belldandy! Please listen!
I have never experienced
any kind of real hardship
the whole time
I've been with you!
After all... as long
as you stay with me...
my wish has already
been granted, hasn't it?
Oh, no...! Our eyes met!
Huh...? Nothing happened...
Oh, Keiichi!
This light...
I can't explain it.
It feels so warm...
What am I...
What was I doing anyway?
I feel like I had a
bad dream or something...
Oh, man... so even I got
caught up in it, too.
Huh?
And where do you
think you're going?
Um... well, you see...
I just remembered
some urgent business.
Right...
Well, before you go, would you
mind telling me one thing?
It wasn't me...!
I did not go into your room,
or take any of your potions,
or try to monopolize
Keiichi's heart!
I never did anything like that!
How could you even accuse
me of such a thing?! Really!
Yes, yes. Of course.
You are a First Class goddess.
You don't know
how to lie, right?
Well, anyway...
For a minute there I didn't
know what was going to happen.
Oh yeah? Well,
how do you think I felt?
And now Belldandy's out like
a light because of all this.
Hey, Urd...
Why didn't the potion
Peorth gave me
have any affect at
all on Belldandy?
I think that should
be pretty obvious.
My potions aren't so
unromantic as to affect
a couple who really
do love each other.
--Oh...
--Mm...!
Hey, you know, I haven't seen
Peorth around in a while.
Ah, yes... well,
actually Peorth is, uh...
Honestly, you are SO quiet.
I really wish you wouldn't make
me do all of the talking here!
I mean, you and I are
already on very good terms
with one another, aren't we?
I'll do even more
for you, too...
Come on... tell me
what you want...
How I love that little,
round nose...! It's adorable!
And you have such a
charming little belly, too...
Oh, you lovely little
pot-bellied tanuki, you!
Tanook-ee-ookie-doo! I love you!
The truth is... It should
have been a fun first date.
In order to overcome the
burden of a past mistake,
the goddess takes
on an old challenge.
Next time, "Ah! The Goddesses
Go Head to Head on a Date."
Bringing down meteors is
going a little overboard here!