Three-twelve, and
another two-seventy,
plus one-twenty-five...
and that brings your total
to nine forty-one, Sir.
Right... and that'll be
out of ten dollars...
Here's your change.
And please visit us again soon!
Yeah... I-I will!
Next in line, please! I'm so
sorry to have kept you waiting.
Hey! I'm open.
Can I help the next
customer over here?
I made us some tea.
Hey, that's great...
thanks a lot.
Ah... I wonder if
it's going to make
the Almighty One
angry because...
I let a goddess like you
do all this kind of work.
Don't worry.
I'm sure it is fine...
Because being together with you
is something that I wished for.
And I think the way that
time flows from day to day
is actually quite
beautiful to see.
I am so glad that I came down
here to Earth to live with you!
It is thanks to you
that I am able to enjoy
seeing all these things.
Simply being here
together with you
makes it fun, Mr. Keiichi!
Thank you, Santa!
Man... I can't believe it's
Christmas time already...
Christmas time...
what is that?
Each year on the night
of December 24th...
this guy named Santa Claus
travels around the world,
coming to every home and leaving
presents for all the children.
My, there certainly are
some wonderful people
living here on Earth,
aren't there?
Well, it's actually the
children's fathers or mothers
who leave the gifts...
So you mean that people
here on the surface world
call their parents
"Santa Claus"?
No... that's not what I meant...
It's just one of those things
we make a big production out of,
and most kids know the truth.
Oh, I see. So that is how it is?
Belldandy has been with
me for almost a year now.
And in all that time, I haven't
done a single thing for her
that a boyfriend should do.
Like buying her a
Christmas present...
But what on Earth would
make Belldandy happy?
Hey Mister!
Oh, hi there, Hijiri.
Looky, looky! I got
this from Santa Claus!
My, that is a very
pretty balloon.
Uh...
Hijiri... what kind of
Christmas present
do you suppose would
really make a girl happy?
I mean, besides a balloon.
A ring!
Whenever we walk by this
store, my Mommy always
looks in the window and says,
"Isn't that ring lovely?"
Oh, I see.
Mommy's waiting
for me, so I gotta go.
See ya later! Bye-bye!
Belldandy?
Yes?
Do you like... these rings?
They are very pretty,
aren't they?
Okay...
So, that means you do like them?
Yes, I like them very much.
Is that so...
Why do you ask, Mr. Keiichi?
Um, well... I was wondering if
there's anything you might want
right now?
Anything I might
want right now...?
Well, let me think...
Ah...! Yes, there is!
What?
I can't believe she
actually gets excited
over something like that.
Well, you know...
It's typical Belldandy.
Thank you so much.
I had completely
forgotten we were out.
No problem. I'm just
glad it made you happy.
But that's still not gonna cut
it for a Christmas present...
So, Keiichi...
What are you gonna get me for
a Christmas present, huh?!
What do you have on your
list this year, Skuld?
Although it should really
go without saying...
I want a monkey wrench,
ignition spanner set,
an electric drill,
and some cryo wire!
Now I'm sorry that I asked.
Hey! What's that
supposed to mean?
All right, all right. I'm sorry!
They're way too much
for me to afford...
Even though I really would
like to get one of these
for Belldandy...
--Buy it...
--Huh?
Buy the ring...
It's... talking!
Buy one...
It's like it's calling to me!
The way it's shiny...
The way it glitters...
That's right...! Now this
will definitely make her...
Yes, buy it...! Buy it for Urd!
You know you want to!
What do you think you're doing?
Uh-oh!
Seeing as how you're
agonizing here,
I thought I'd give
you some good advice.
I'm not "agonizing."
Oh, aren't you...?
That sparkly ring would look so
nice on her soft dainty finger,
now wouldn't it?
Yeah, it would...
You see, receiving a ring
from the one she loves
is the greatest happiness that
a girl could ever experience.
The greatest happiness?
That's right!
Uh... is it really?
Yes. It's because
you can truly sense
the feelings of
the person you love
every time you put the
ring on your finger.
It's utterly divine.
Is that true, Urd?
Come on, you can trust me.
You're right...
I do want Belldandy
to be able to sense
my feelings for her in
the same way I can feel hers
through this sweater
that she made for me!
That's it then.
If you are bound together by
true love, that ring is a must.
You need to buy it
right this minute!
Yeah... let's do it.
I'll go buy it right now!
Come on, just go ahead and
splurge on it, Keiichi.
But just one of these
rings is equal to
four months of my
living expenses...
And here I just told
someone that it's
what's in a person's
heart that counts.
All right, if you think
she's not worth it.
Hey, it's Morisato!
Hey, guys.
When did we ever teach
you to be the kinda guy
to stand around in
a place like this,
looking at ladies' jewelry?!
That's right!
You oughta break
a sweat with us
doing some part-time work!
Uh... I will!
Please help me get a job
wherever it is you're doing!
Uh... okay.
Aw, geez!
All I wanted was for you guys to
help me get some part-time work!
Don't' be ridiculous!
Everyone knows that
working aboard a fishing
boat is man's work!
You forge both mind and body,
and earn money
while you're at it.
Two birds with one stone!
All right, fine. But
I just have one question.
I will be able to go home
right after this, right?
Well, yeah, three
months from now...
Three months! It'll be
way too late by then!
So what? After we get back,
you'll be able to buy
ten or twenty rings easy!
Somebody help me!
Oh, boy. He sure has
a long way to go...
I should've known it was a
mistake to rely on those two.
Just four days left
'til Christmas Eve.
I guess the only way
I can pull this off
is to find another part-time
job somewhere else,
but where am I gonna find one?
What are you trying to find?
Ah...! Nothing! Nothing at all!
Oh, okay then...
Well since I worked
the earlier shift today,
I'll go home ahead of you and
get dinner ready, Mr. Keiichi.
Uh... Sure...
Uh, wait just a
minute, Belldandy.
Yes?
I've got some stuff
I need to take care of,
so I'll be getting home late
the next three or four days.
All right.
I don't think we're gonna be
able to eat dinner together,
and I probably won't be able to
spend much time at the
house with you either...
Okay, I understand.
Don't you even want to know why?
No, because I trust you.
You mean you aren't worried?
You are not going to be doing
anything dangerous, are you?
No, it's nothing like that!
Then there's no need
for me to worry.
Man, it looks like the only
sorta jobs that'll get me
that kind of fast money
are all pretty dreadful.
I guess making two thousand
bucks in only four days
might be asking too much.
"I trust you," huh?
So, you've made up
your mind, have you?!
What are you just
sitting around for?
Come on, kid! It's time
for you to go to work!
Huh?!
He's got some nerve
keeping secrets!
What could he possibly
be up to anyway?
I wonder...
And Urd isn't at home either.
Those two are totally up
to something, I know it...!
Huh?
The miso soup has gotten cold,
so I'll go warm it up.
But Big Sis!
Please don't worry, Skuld.
I have complete
trust in Mr. Keiichi.
Hey, is there anything I
can help you with, Big Sis?
Why thank you very much, Skuld!
Would you like to chop up
these onions for me?
No problem!
All right. Knock yourself out!
Not tuna again.
Well, they say
the longest journey
begins with a single step.
I had a rather difficult
time finding you a job
that pays well, you know.
I'll bet you the Auto Club guys
tipped you off about this,
didn't they?
Hmph!
Go on, full speed
ahead to the ring!
Get a move on, Keiichi.
And be sure to give it your all.
Okay... I'll give it my all...!
Aaaachoo!
All that work, and only a
hundred bucks to show for it...
Stop whining!
I'm back!
Welcome home!
Whoa...!
I had a feeling you'd be
coming home right about now.
A total lie...! She's been
waiting the whole time!
Is that true, Belldandy?
Yes, but please don't worry.
We goddesses exist
for the purpose
of bringing you
happiness, Mr. Keiichi.
That is my responsibility.
Yeah, well, happiness for me
is getting to help
my big sister out!
Go ahead and eat your dinner
while it is still warm, okay?
Thanks for making this for me.
I'm gonna give it
my all tomorrow, too!
Here, take one!
Here you go. Thanks!
Have some of this, Mr. Keiichi.
Thanks a lot.
Please don't push
yourself too hard, okay?
Hey, don't worry about me.
I think I'm gonna
be just fine...
You know why Mr. Keiichi
has been coming home
so late every night, don't you?
I worried because
he seems so exhausted.
Please Urd...
was it something you
said to Mr. Keiichi?
Well, I certainly did help
the kid get fired up...
but what Keiichi's
doing right now
is entirely of
his own free will.
So maybe we should just
let him do as he pleases.
Right.
I trust him completely.
Man, I feel like I haven't
had a decent conversation
with Belldandy in days.
I wonder if she's mad
at me for going so far
to keep this a secret from her.
Are you all right?
Hey, Urd.
Yeah...?
Do you think it's wrong...
for me to be keeping everything
a secret from Belldandy?
Hang on, you do want to
surprise her, don't you?
Yeah... But, she's not
asking me any questions,
she's just waiting
patiently for me.
And now it's like I'm
starting to wonder if
this ring is gonna
even convey my feelings.
Well if that's how you feel,
maybe you should just give up.
Hm?
Belldandy trusts you,
and she's waiting for you.
And you feel you need to
reciprocate that, correct?
Mm-hm...
True, money won't
buy someone's heart...
but it's your feelings for her
that have brought you this far.
If you've made up your mind,
then see this
through to the end.
You are a man, aren't you?
All right.
I'm gonna give it my all.
For Belldandy!
Ah...!
Are you all right?!
I did it!
If I add up what I've already
made to tomorrow's earnings,
it'll be enough! Thank you, Urd!
You're the one who
did all the hard work.
I only got you the jobs.
Well, that might be true...
but you definitely
helped me out a lot.
You can pay me back
after you get the ring.
You did a really
good job, Keiichi.
And I'm sure she's going
to be delighted with it.
Now, gather your courage and
tell Belldandy how you feel.
Right!
Big Sis? Big Sis!
Oh...! Yes, Skuld, what is it?
The miso soup has
gotten cold again.
Oh... so it has...
Well I had better go
and warm it up then.
Hey, I'm back!
Sorry I'm so late
again, Belldandy.
Welcome home, Mr. Keiichi.
Belldandy...
Thanks again for
making me dinner.
Belldandy...
Yes, what is it?
I'm really sorry to have worried
you so much like I have...
But, I'll be done with all
of this tomorrow, okay?
I'm very glad to hear it.
You haven't said a thing,
even though I've been...
keeping secrets from you.
You have already told me
everything that you
were able to, correct?
Or have you possibly
been doing something
that you shouldn't have?
No, I haven't!
I see you've been wearing the
sweater I gave you every day.
Therefore, I am able to
rest easy every night
because I know you've
worn the sweater yet again.
It is saying that our
feelings are still connected.
And so--
Eight O'clock!
Tomorrow night at eight!
I want you to wait for me in
front of the train station then.
At eight o'clock?
Yes, there's something there
I want to show you, Belldandy.
Right!
I did it!
Hey, you did such
a good job, kid,
I even threw in a little
extra for ya there.
Oh, thank you very much!
I've got it made!
Honestly, you're the
one who helped us out.
The end of the year's
always really hectic for us.
Let's get a move on, Keiichi.
Oh, right!
All right, Belldandy.
I'll be able to give
it to you really soon,
so just hang on
a little longer.
Wha?! It's gone!
And after I worked so hard
to earn enough money for it!
Are you sure this is the
one you wanted, Madam?
I guess.
I'll... just put that
on my credit card...
AAAHH!
But, Sayoko, you don't
understand. That ring was...
What...?
Please don't tell me that
you've already bought it!
Yeah, and so what if I have...?
So that's it, is it?
Come on... Sayoko...
Please. I'm asking you to
let me buy that ring instead!
I see, so Keiichi would like to
buy a ring now, is that right?
Oh, wait!
Could it be you mean to give
it to me as a present...?
I'm so happy!
As if he'd really buy it for
a little trollop like YOU!
You see this...?
I'm begging you now.
I'll do anything
you want, please.
What the hell are you doing?!
Please, Sayoko!
Keiichi!
All right then.
What? You mean it?!
Not so fast...
There's one condition.
I want you to make up for
having spoiled my Christmas.
Look, Mommy! It's Santa!
So, why am I dressed
up like a reindeer?
I think it suits you.
Merry Christmas everyone!
It is Christmas time, so these
outfits make perfect sense.
You will shine them.
Are you really asking a goddess
to give you a shoeshine...?!
Who the hell do
you think you are?!
Let's see...
Well, other than being a queen,
then perhaps I'm a devil, too.
So... what do you
want me to do anyway?
I think...
Waaah...! I lost
my balloon, Mommy!
I'll buy you a new
one, sweetheart.
Uh-uh! I like that one, mommy!
Why don't you go get it?
HUH?!
You're Santa, so you
should be comfortable
dealing with heights, right?
Now you're being unreasonable!
All right.
But... if I do get it down,
you'll let me have
the ring, right?
Fine! It's a deal.
I wonder where he is...
Please stop this, Keiichi...!
Why don't you just
let me get it for you?!
Mr. Keiichi!
Huh?!
It is too dangerous!
Please come back down!
Belldandy?!
Please come down now!
I'll be all right... Just wait
right there, Belldandy.
Be careful!
A little closer...
I've almost got it...
Ooooh!
Gotcha!
Hey, I did it, Belldandy...!
Whoa! AAAAHHH!
Oh, Spirit of the Wind who
summons the great tempest...
Air Bug Spiral!
Aaaahhh!
Oh... brother...
Mr. Keiichi!
Why would you ever go and
do such a reckless thing?!
The balloon...
It just flew away.
Huh?
I meant to buy you
a Christmas present,
but it looks like it's
not going to pan out...
after all that.
I am more concerned about you
than anything else, Mr. Keiichi!
I really did give it
my all this time
to try to show you
my feelings...
but, as usual, you ended up
having to save me once again.
I admit that it wasn't
going to be the same
as the hand-knitted
sweater you made for me,
but still, I was working
as hard as I could
to try and somehow give
shape to my true feelings...
but I've failed you again.
Mm-mm... it's not
like that at all.
You were working hard
and coming home late
exhausted every night...
because of me...
I want to be with you,
because that is how you are.
And that is why I love you
so much, Mr. Keiichi.
Here.
Huh?
That's... the ring...
Yeah, she decided
to give it over.
But she...
And in exchange,
she said she wants you to
provide some entertainment
at a party she's throwing.
HUH...?!
All right. Get on with it!
Is that...?
I thought it would
look good on you.
Oh, I love it!
Here, give me your hand.
All right!
Mr. Keiichi!
Hm? Snow?
Wow...
Thank you, my Santa Claus...
The goddess wishes for
happiness all over the world.
He wonders if it's okay for him
to have the goddess
all to himself.
Next time, "Ah! I Want to Fill
the World with Happiness."
Hey, lucky you, Hasegawa...