These Japanese hot springs...
are just so nice...
You said it... And this
sake is great, too.
That's all you ever
care about, Urd!
Hm! Don't be so up-tight.
I mean, it's been so long since
we've had a nice bath together.
And that's all thanks to Big Sis
winning us a free trip
to the hot springs.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Uh... You mean you didn't?
I'm afraid not.
Huh?
Oh, well... who cares?!
Oh, and by the way, Skuld, looks
like you've grown a little!
Hey, c'mon!
Wait a min-- stop it!
Urd, I'm serious! Big Sis!
Get her off me! Leave me alone!
What's a woman doing
in the men's bath?!
Mm...
--Mara!
--Huh?
M-Morisato?
Uh... Uh...
Huh?
Are you okay, Keiichi?
Uh yeah, I guess
I'll be all right...
I can't believe a demon
would scream like that
over being seen
naked by a human!
I couldn't help it!
I was taken by surprise!
I mean, I never expected
to see the four of you here!
Mon Amour, what lies ahead in
life is shrouded in darkness.
No one knows what lies to
come at the end of the tunnel!
So much for be able to relax
and enjoy the hot spring.
--Way to screw things up!
--Are you serious?
You mean you weren't planning to
pull another nasty trick on us?
I'm taking some personal time...
I don't intend to
get into it with you.
Then how about a drink?
It's been a while.
--A drink?!
--Huh?
Hey, it's your day off, right?
We used to drink a lot
together back before
we were in this line of work.
Uh, yeah, I guess you're right.
Hey, hey, Mara...
So those two used to be close?
Yes. I'm sure they
still are, too.
That's surprising!
I never would've guessed that.
I think maybe...
There's a connection
between them after all.
This reminds me of how
you put a bug in my drink
that one time.
Oh, yeah.
But that was in return for
the poison you put in my drink
that other time.
Are you sure those two really
have a close friendship...?
After that, we made up with each
other by exchanging flowers.
That's right, and we both put
exploding roses in the bouquets.
Well, it certainly seems to me
like we have a score
to settle after all.
Yes, it would seem so.
--Grr...!
--Oh, I have an idea.
--Huh?
Well, what is it?
As long as we're here, we'll
forget about being "goddesses"
or "demons", and we won't get
into any fights, no matter what.
And if anyone breaks
this rule, then...
...she'll be severely punished!
Uh...
Jeez! I'm just being myself.
I don't even want to think
what the punishment could be.
Are we all agreed then?
--Agreed.
Okay, then let's
all have some fun!
I used to go to the
firing range every day
to shoot away the gloom I
felt when you defeated me.
You'd be nuts to think
you can defeat me now!
Okay, next game!
Aw... too bad. You're only
about 99 million points
short of being able
to compete with me.
SEE!
I don't have time for
ridiculous games like this!
I've had it!
Oh, I see...
Are you saying you'd rather
settle things like THIS?
It would be a pleasure.
I guess violence is out of
the question, though...!
After all, nothing ever comes
from meaningless fighting!
Oh, yeah! She's right!
How about we have a nice, fun
game of ping-pong next, huh?
Hey, and there's always
karaoke, ya know!
Well, now that you mention it,
there's always mahjong!
Yeah, mahjong would be
great, or a nice game of...
Good grief, they've
got a lot of energy!
I guess Mara is a lot more
fun than I had expected.
Yes... she really is.
--Yeah! All right!
--Woohoo!
I wonder when the next time
we drink together will be.
Urd...! Hurry up, we're leaving!
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, I want the
window seat, Big Sis!
Take care, Mara.
Move over! I want to
sit next to Big Sis!
It ain't easy to
fake being drunk.
Ya know...
If only Urd weren't a
goddess and I weren't a demon...
then every day could be
like this. However...
Senbei!
At your service, and
refreshingly pleasant as ever.
Were you able to get me
a strand of her hair?
Oui, Milady...! I was
able to obtain one with
the greatest of ease in that
tres magnifique outdoor bath.
Well, well, well...
The fun is just beginning, Urd.
What are you going
to do about this?!
I was almost
finished with it, too!
Look, I already
told you I'm sorry!
All I did was trip over that
stupid bomb, and it broke.
It's not a "stupid bomb!"
It's a machine for reaching
stuff in high places!
Oh, is that right?
I guess that'd be a
necessity for you...
There they go again...
Sorry about that, kiddo.
I guess I can see
why you're so upset!
URD, YOU BIG JERK!
DON'T EVER SHOW
YOUR FACE HERE AGAIN!
Oh, are you going out?
I can't handle being
around her right now,
so I'm gonna take off for a bit.
See you later then.
Do me a favor and go console
our little sister, okay?
I just don't have
the patience right now.
Appreciate it!
Talk about irresponsible...
I mean she's the one who upset
Skuld in the first place!
--It's not that...
--Huh?
It's just that it's
Urd's way of showing
that she really cares about her.
You think so, huh?
Yes, I do.
Thank you very much.
Hm...
That was pretty generous of me.
Uh!
Well, I guess I'll go buy some
ingredients for my potions
and head back.
Do it.
Sí! Just leave it to moi, dear.
Shakkin!
Talk about the oldest
trick in the book...
Enka... music?!
So, how do you like
my cursed headphones?
Mara...
How careless of me...
Just... when I thought...
Now why don't we take a look
at tomorrow's weather forecast?
We should be having
a lot of sunny weather
all around the country.
--Hey, where's Urd?
--Not back yet.
Well, she's certainly
out pretty late tonight.
Probably just out
having fun somewhere.
Still, it's kinda weird for her
not to at least give us a call.
I don't care if she
doesn't come home ever.
I guess it's all right...
I mean, Urd's a big girl.
I suppose she can take
care of herself, huh?
Ah...! Look, I told you!
I'm not worried about her!
Oh... Keiichi! Something
terrible has happened!
You see... I found
this bag of ice cream
near the drugstore
while I was out shopping.
I could sense Urd's
presence still on it...
Huh?!
I'll try to call forth any
residual thoughts it holds.
Oh, spirits of earth and air
who watch over us always...
Hear my voice!
That was pretty generous of me.
So then, this really was Urd's?
Then did she actually
buy this ice cream?
--Ahh!
Uh, w-what the heck was that?!
Look, it's Mara.
I'll bet that she managed
to put her to sleep
by forcing her to
listen to Enka!
Huh?! You're saying she's
been captured by Mara?!
I'm afraid so...
How could she...
I mean, we had so much fun
together the other day!
Skuld!
Hey, Banpei!
Geez! Urd, you're such a pain!
You're always putting me
through all this trouble.
Uh...
Hold on...
What is going on here?!
Are you referring to your
current predicament?
Or are you referring to this,
which I cultivated using
a strand of your hair.
A clone of me?!
I see...
So that's why you palled
around with us at the resort.
Very good! You know, that's
what I like that about you.
How quickly you
pick up on things.
You're nuts if you think
you can get anywhere
with that half-baked thing.
Quite true...!
Right now, it's nothing more
than a mere soulless doll.
That is exactly why I
had to bring you here...
So that I could separate
your divine half
from your demon half...
and then transplant
it into HER!
Oh, please. As if...
Why not?
Because, Mara, even
you should know...
not even the Almighty One
could separate my divine half
from my demonic half.
Hmph!
Well, it just so happens
that I have obtained this.
Huh?
A legendary item which can
split and fuse personalities.
Gaze upon the heretical pot!
Mara, tell me...
Where did you get that?
From Hell's mail-order catalog!
Hey, I haven't seen you
around here before.
Ah, well, I'm new.
Is that so? Huh?!
Hey, wait! I never
ordered this thing!
But, that's definitely what
I got on the invoice here.
Well... I guess so...
Hey, thanks, we
appreciate your business!
So, what the heck IS this thing?
This is the legendary
heretical pot,
which I can use to split
and fuse personalities
however I please, and
which came mixed in
with a number of
items that I bought
through Hell's
mail-order catalog!
See how fortune smiles upon me
for all the good I've done!
Don't you use that ceramic
piece of junk on me!
Commence transplant!
Come on, baby... let's go!
The battery's run down, huh?
Oh... please, Urd...
Don't tell me you
really did get caught.
I wish I hadn't told her
to never come back.
Oh, Urd...! Where the
heck have you gone?!
What are you doing here, Skuld?
Huh?! Urd, you're back!
I was so worried about you!
I thought Mara might have
sealed you away or something!
You silly girl... I assure you
that would never happen.
You see...
Huh?!
You're the one who's
going to be sealed away.
So, how do you like
being able to see
the stupid look on your face
while you're being sealed?
Why are you doing this, Urd?!
Is it because I told you
never to come back?
Not a bit... It's just that
I'm sick of you, that's all.
NO...!
It's too bad for you, Skuld.
Unfortunately, you
won't get the chance
to see Belldandy getting sealed.
Why'd you seal her away?
Because she's a nuisance.
That wasn't part of the plan!
Sealing the goddesses
was never my intention!
My real mission is to
increase demonic shares
by encouraging those who
are blessed by the goddesses
into accepting
contracts with devils,
which come closer fulfilling
human desires anyway.
Hmph!
So basically, as long
as the goddesses go home now,
I'm good!
You're naïve - simple.
What's that?!
If increasing shares
is what you want to do,
then take the whole world!
What?!
Take over the whole world?!
Oh, how wonderful!
A free world
without law and order!
Truly, a utopia for humanity!
And you,
my lovely Mara, will
go down in history
as the greatest
of all demons...
You will be known
as the legendary one
who brought the whole
Earth under demonkind!
Besides... this is
such a simple seal,
even you could undo it
in a snap if you wanted to.
Ah, but I'm not authorized to.
The higher-ups would be...
Do you really think anyone is
going to question the great hero
that conquered the world
that nobody else could?
The rest is yours to decide.
All right! I'm gonna do it!
Oh, yeah, baby!
What a moron.
Even though it is a simple
seal, only I can undo it.
I suspect I can make use of her
for a little while anyway.
Until I, Demonic Urd,
become the ruler of Earth.
Let's go! For the
glory of demonkind!
--Hip, hip, hooray!
--Yeah! Hooray!
--Banzai!
I searched and searched, but
I still couldn't find them...
I'll bet Mara really has
gotten a hold of those two.
It'll be all right.
I mean think about it...
We don't have any proof
that Urd and Skuld
have been kidnapped by Mara.
But Keiichi...
Besides, my intuition
is usually spot-on...
in situations like this...
Uh... Sorry! I guess
that's not really something
I should be telling a goddess!
Well, thank you.
Uh...! Jeez... I'm sorry.
I can't think of
anything better to say.
No, really, it's okay.
I'll just go in and
make us some tea for us.
This is not good. I need
to get a hold of myself.
Why can't I say anything to
comfort her at a time like this?
That's pretty sad, even for me.
--Urd, you're back!
--Huh?
Hey, you two. Welcome home.
Hey, Urd!
Oh... I'm just so glad
that you're all right!
Mara said she wanted
revenge on me
for the last time we hung out,
so she had me out drinking
with her all night.
Thank goodness.
I was so very worried
about you, Urd!
Oh, Belldandy. I'm so sorry.
By the way, has Skuld come back?
Oh, I guess not.
On the way home, I saw
Banpei just lying around,
so I brought him home.
I should go back out
and look for her!
Then I'll go with you, as well!
No, no, no! We want somebody
here in case she comes back.
You two wait here!
You're next... Belldandy.
Oh, where am I?
Let's see...
The last thing I remember
I had been tricked and
captured by Mara...
--Somebody! Please help me!
--Huh?
Oh, please!
Isn't this... a mirror
used for sealing souls?
It's just so sad...
It seems somebody has been
locked away inside of it.
It couldn't be...!
Key that locks the seal,
hear now my voice and respond.
I am the master of the seal...
I am the source of liberation.
Hear now my command
and release she
who is ensnared within!
Aaahh!
Hey, that really hurt!
Couldn't you have done
that a little-- huh?
Urd?!
NO! Don't seal me away again!
--I'm so sorry!
--Huh...?
Come again? WHAAAT?!
So then you're saying I was
sealed into that mirror
by your demonic half?
Yes...
Given how I was able to release
the seal with my own voice,
it's only natural to assume that
Mara succeeded in separating
my good and evil halves.
And that caused you...
such unbelievable
pain and hardship!
This... is kinda creepy.
Uh...! Wait a sec! So where's
the other you right now?!
--Belldandy's in trouble!
--Big Sis's in trouble!
♪ Black tea, black tea,
la la la la la... ♪
♪ Add a little milk, a touch
of sugar and a lemon... ♪
Keiichi's been sent away,
just as I was hoping.
The rule of evil shall begin
in the most unlikely of places.
--Oh, my!
--Waaahh!
You just couldn't wait
for the tea, could you?
Uh, right! I couldn't!
If I don't have some right away,
it'll only get cold, won't it?
That's true.
Wow, she really
caught me off-guard...
I'll get her this time.
Oh no. I almost forgot to offer
you some cookies with the tea!
Aaah...!
That was a close shave...
What's the matter? You okay?
Sure, cookies...
Yeah, I'd love some.
You mean the crispy,
sweet ones, right?
Sure...! I'll be right
back in a minute.
'Kay...! I'll be waiting!
Damn it, she is a
challenge after all.
She's been blessed with an
innate sense of bad timing.
But...
...this time she's
not getting away.
I almost forgot!
I have to remember to put aside
some cookies for Skuld, too!
Oh, hey! Are you
exercising, Urd?
Just trying to shed some
calories from the food earlier.
Oh, I see.
I've got to hand it to her...
She doesn't have a
shred of common sense.
--I'm home!
--Huh?
Ah! Keiichi!
No way...! He's back already?
Yeah, well... I forgot
to take my helmet.
Oh, dear!
Ugh...
I just can't believe
these two...
Just wait right here.
I'll go get it for you.
At this rate, my
plans'll be ruined.
Oh! Wait a minute...
I can use this to my advantage.
All I really need is an
opening to get at Belldandy.
Hey, Keiichi?
Huh? Yeah, what's up?
Do me a favor and close your
eyes until I count to three.
Huh...? What for?
I was just thinking that
I'd give you a charm
that's going to help you
to find Skuld more quickly.
Hm? Oh, is that all?
Okay then... Let me have it.
Right... One...
He's so unassuming.
Two...
But it's going to cost him.
--Three...
--Mm!
Here you go, Keiichi. Ah!
Urd... What is this?
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?!
Ah!
Ah...
Belldandy! W-Wait!
Silly boy.
Why would Urd do such a thing?
Are you sure about this?
If this chaos continues, my
demonic half and I will both--
Even if you are overcome with
evil, you're still you, Urd.
Next time, "Ah! Shimmer
Without Fear of the Darkness."
Urd! I'll save you
no matter what!
Just forget that you're the
one who started all this...
Huh?