Oh, no. Those poor flowers...
Oh, that's right...
I can't do it that way...
They should feel
much better now!
We'll both have to try
and do our best together.
I still can't believe
that Belldandy's license
has been suspended.
Oh, poor Big Sis...
I feel so bad for her not being
able to use any of her powers!
So I guess that means Belldandy
can't fly anymore either?
Well, at least not
until next week.
What? Only a week?
Yeah, can you believe
a whole week...?!
Even if the Goddess Help Line
decided to reissue her license,
she'd still have to go
all the way back to Heaven
to take a refresher course.
Day after day, she'll be
forced to watch boring videos
then log hours of practice in
the spellcasting simulator.
It's such a pain.
But in your case, didn't
you have to do it for like
fifty years or something?
Yeah, but this is only
her first offense...
So don't worry about it.
Well... I guess a week
really isn't that long.
And besides, I doubt that she--
Oh! We should probably go soon,
so we're not late to class.
Today is Professor
Kakuta's lecture, isn't it?
Uh... Oh, yeah...
Well, she doesn't seem to be
the least bit down about it.
Poor Big Sis...
Huh?
--Hey, Morisato!
Uh... Hey, guys.
Long time, no see.
We have a little
favor to ask of you.
And what might that be?
We've got some stuff
we'd like you to hang onto.
Uh... stuff?
Well, how long do you need
me to hang onto it for?
We need to leave it
here for a week.
Oh, sure... If it's
only a week, no problem.
Hey, everyone...!
He says it's okay!
"Everyone"?
Aghh...
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
--Oh my!
--Thanks for your help!
The dorm's being remodeled,
and we were in a pinch for
somewhere to store our stuff.
Yeah, thanks a bunch.
And sorry to trouble you with
this little inconvenience.
--Nice guy, isn't he?
--You call this little?!
Oh, brother!
Now, look here, Keiichi!
So what do we do
with all this stuff?!
Hey, don't look at me!
It's not like any of you stood
up and said anything either!
Sorry, but Tamiya's
problems are your problems.
And who may I ask decided that?
Well, I did of course, just now.
You did, huh?
Well that's just great.
Well... I guess we can just
stick it in the main temple
if we have to.
Huh?!
Hey Kei! Sorry to bother you,
but I just bought a new
refrigerator, washing machine,
and kotatsu table, so...
could you store my old ones
until the garbage
collector comes?
Mm!
Hi there! I just got these two
rare bikes in good condition
for a steal at an auction,
but then realized, I've got
nowhere to put them.
Can I leave them here until
I've cleaned out my garage?
I'll come get them,
along with these boxes,
as soon as I'm done.
Oh!
It seems I've gone and
bought too many clothes...
and now my storage rooms are
full to the point of bursting.
Would you mind
hanging onto these
until we've completed
the new addition?
All right...
Just because they ask,
doesn't mean you have to take
EVERYONE'S stuff, you know!
I know, but...
I'm sorry, Keiichi.
If I hadn't had my
license suspended,
I'd be able to shrink
all these things
so they wouldn't take up
quite so much room...
Oh, Big Sis... Don't worry!
Just leave everything to me!
So, do you have
some kind of plan?
First, gather all
the stuff in one place,
and then I'll tell you
the rest of the plan.
Oh. Why do I have a
bad feeling about this?
Okay, the question before us is:
Why haven't we been able to
straighten this place up?
Because we don't
have enough room?
Correct!
So, therefore...
the solution is simply
to make more space.
But even the temple building
is almost completely full.
Mr. Morisato! Were you
listening to what I said?
I said that we're going to
need to make more space.
Make-more-space.
What the heck is that?!
It's my Space-doubler.
I'll show you how it works.
Magnification, on.
Then you simply increase the
function area by six times.
Confirm changes... And start!
Gaah!
What did you do, Skuld?!
The room just got a lot bigger!
Because I made more space.
"Made" more space...?
How did you do that?
I guess you could say I
took out an "advanced loan."
If you think about it...
One hour or two hours from now,
this will still be the
exact same space, right?
So I've effectively increased
the size of the present space
by sliding that
future space into it!
I can't say it totally get it,
but it's pretty amazing.
Well, in any case, we've got
ourselves some more room now...
All right, time for us
to start straighten up!
Hey!
They ran off. What a surprise.
Um, Keiichi... I'll try
and help out the best I can.
Thanks, Belldandy,
I really appreciate it!
Well, I guess I
should be grateful
that at least I've got
somewhere to put all this stuff.
--Keiichi!
--Huh?
So where... should
I put this... thing?
Whoa, careful!
Don't strain yourself!
Ahh!
Belldandy!
My powers... Oh, no! I mustn't!
If I use a spell
during my suspension,
my license will be revoked!
I'm so sorry, Keiichi.
It's okay.
Eeeh!
Well, then!
I guess I better just go ahead
and move this box over here!
You're amazing, Keiichi.
Huh? Not really...
I think of you as
the amazing one.
Oh, no... I've become
quite powerless
now that my license
has been suspended
and I can no longer
use any spells.
But even without any powers,
you always manage to be amazing.
Well, let's stop worrying
about who's more amazing
and just focus on
getting this stuff moved.
Ah... All right!
Except... we're already
running out of space again, huh?
Well, how 'bout we just
open up a little more room?
Let's see now...
I think it turns that way.
Is that how it went?
Uh... I think she said...
press the magnification
mode first,
and then the
function area, right?
Uh, which one is it?
Let's see...
Right! I think that
should set it...
What's wrong...? Isn't that it?
"Please select your options"?
I don't remember
anything like that.
Are you sure you're pressing
the correct button, Keiichi?
You see?
Oh yeah! You're right! Okay!
So then I just put the value
of the area ratio here...
Okay! Let's see
if this works!
AAHH!
Uh... Ah!
Ah!
So... Let's see if those
two're any further along
than when I last
checked on them.
Uh?
Huh...?! The whole room?!
Big Sis!
Hm?!
Waaaahh!
Belldandy! Keiichi!
It's no use.
It looks like it's been expanded
into an almost
infinite dimension...
There's no way your
voice can reach them.
"Infinite dimension?"
Uh...
Where the heck... is the EXIT?!
I never thought that
the Space-doubler
would go out of control.
Hey... can't you just
reset that thing?
Well, yeah, it's
possible, but...
you've gotta press UP, UP, DOWN,
DOWN, LEFT, RIGHT, LEFT, RIGHT
and then finally
press the "set" button
twice before it will reset!
And can Keiichi do that?
I seriously doubt it.
All right, fine. I'll just
go in and do it myself.
--That won't work.
--Hm?
How exactly do you plan
to find them in there?
Big Sis is forbidden
from using her powers
while she's under
suspension. Remember?
And since she can't
use her powers...
we won't be able to
find any energy surges
to trace her by, huh?
If only we at least
knew where she was...
Well, it's not that we don't
know where they are in there...
Huh?
She's definitely in the
center of this space.
Because the Space-doubler
expands space outwards
from where it is.
Well, that makes things
easy, doesn't it?
Yeah. Assuming we could
find out where the center IS.
Huh?
You see... There's no way
for us to find the center
of this infinite dimension.
You also have to remember that
this is an emulated space.
If you got lost in this,
you'd never be able to find
your way back out again.
Then... we might as well
not even know
where they are at all.
Isn't there anything we can do?
It's no use... We don't even
know which way we're going.
I guess there's no point in
walking around aimlessly then.
I guess not...
Is something wrong?
Well... I don't know
if it's because
you've been suspended
from using your powers...
but you look kind of worn out.
I'll be fine as long as
I know you're all right.
Oh, yeah, I'm doing great.
Besides, I'm used
to all the seniors
always putting me
through the ringer!
Oh, I see.
Well, if this is
the way it is,
I guess there's nothing
we can do. Ah...!
I mean it's not that
often we just get to
kick back and relax
together, right?
Let's just take it easy
and wait to be rescued.
Keiichi...
It's quiet, isn't it?
Yes, amazingly quiet.
So, you're not bored at all?
No... I really don't mind
spending time like this
doing nothing at all...
In fact, I rather enjoy it.
Actually... I'm starting
to think that maybe
I'm the one who's bored.
Well, maybe we should
come up with something
to pass the time then?
Yeah, okay.
Let's think of something fun
that just the two of us can do.
Y'know... to distract
ourselves for a little while.
That sounds like fun!
So what does that
thing run on, anyway?
Batteries.
How long can they
keep it running?
About a week.
Even if we waited for
the power to run out,
Belldandy would be fine, but
Keiichi won't last that long.
I wouldn't be too
worried about Keiichi.
I'm sure he'll be fine in there,
no matter what happens.
And why's that?
Well, because Big Sis is in
there with him! Of course!
Oh... of course.
Just because Big Sis
is suspended
doesn't mean she
can't use powers,
just that she's not supposed to.
So, despite the consequences,
she could use
them if she had to.
Well, since it's Belldandy
we're talking about...
I'm sure she would do it
if Keiichi were in
some kind of danger.
Even if it meant that she
would lose her license
as a first-class goddess.
Yeah...
Hm... a spice, huh?
Okay, lemme see... Oh, nutmeg!
Nutmeg? Um... egg...
Oh! Eggplant Souffle!
Nice try... but I'm not sure
that qualifies as a seasoning.
Oh, dear...
Maybe try thinking of things
that are less fancy.
I'm sorry.
All right...
Well, why don't we move on to
a different category then...
like animals?
Okay!
Just remember to keep
it simple this time.
I will!
So, have you come
up with anything?
Uh... I know...!
Why don't you make a machine
that'll advance time one week,
but only in this space?
Yeah, I suppose I could
build something like that.
But it would take me at least
six days to put it together.
Oh... Not much use in that then.
You said it...
Does it hurt, Keiichi?
No... not at all, really.
Well, I'm going to go in a
little deeper then, all right?
Mm-hm.
Now I want you to
stay very still for me.
Okay! It's all clean!
Now, let's have a look
at your other ear.
Huh? Oh, okay... Go ahead.
I've been wondering how long
this dimension might end up
staying the way that it is.
Probably not too much longer.
Maybe an hour or two...
Ah! I'm sure Urd and Skuld
will figure out a
way to get us out!
But, what if it turns
out to be longer?
What if we end up being stuck
in here for several days?
You might not be able to...
I'll be fine.
It's not like I haven't
been totally broke
and forced to go a few
days without food before.
So, I know I can at
least handle that much!
But... I don't think
I could handle it.
I just wouldn't be able to
bear it. To see you like that...
But, Belldandy...
I'm sure that I'd eventually use
my powers in order to save you.
Even if it meant losing
my license as a goddess.
I would do it in a heartbeat.
Do you really have such
little faith in me?
In times like these,
I want you to be able to trust
that we'll figure it out.
What do you mean?
We can't let ourselves get
discouraged. That's all!
I know someone
will save us.
As long as we truly
believe in each other,
then the door will open
for us when the time comes.
You really are the most amazing
person I've ever met, Keiichi.
Huh?
I felt... so anxious before.
Until now, I've wanted
to get closer to you,
and I've tried to use my
powers as little as possible.
I really wouldn't have cared
if I had lost my
abilities altogether.
Or so I thought anyway...
Ah, Belldandy...
But, now...
it feels almost like I've been
stripped of a part of myself.
By having my powers
restricted for the first time,
I feel I'm able to appreciate
and learn about your strengths
all over again...
As well as my own
personal weaknesses...
I'm sorry.
I guess I figured we'd
be able to manage fine
for a week
or so out here...
but I didn't consider
how difficult it must be
for you to be
without your powers.
I mean... I can just
stay the way I am now
without ever changing...
Y'see... No matter what happens,
I may never be able to truly
understand your pain, ever.
Oh, Keiichi...
That's why... from now on,
I won't ever take your
feelings for granted.
Belldandy, I'll always
be by your side.
Although, I have to say...
At the moment I
feel pretty useless.
Not at all! You couldn't
be any more encouraging!
Mm...
Be-Be-Be- Belldandy!
Ah!
Would you like to dance?
Huh?!
I know, why not make two
machines that can advance time
by three days each?
I could build each
of those in two days,
so that'd only be
four days altogether!
Keiichi can deal with
the hunger until then!
But Big Sis would
never be able to handle
seeing him like that.
You're right...
I can't use my powers...
but this much I can manage.
Hey, we danced like this
one time back at school.
When we were competing
with Sayoko. Do you remember?
I remember back then...
But I wasn't able
to dance very well.
You know, this reminds me of
the "folk dance" we used to do
during our field days at school.
Was it fun?
Yeah.
Hang on just a little
longer, Lysander.
Meow!
Hello!
I accidentally put my kitty's
food in with the packages
that I gave you guys earlier,
so I was kinda
hoping to get it back.
I afraid that now isn't
really a good time for that.
Meow!
--So where exactly is my stuff?
--Huh?!
Maybe if I just asked
Morisato or Bell they'd know--
I'm telling you that now
is not the time for this!
MEE-YOW!
--Hey there...! Morisato!
--Ah...!
The founder of the
Auto Club's here!
I'm warning you...
So, are Bell and Morisato
even home today or what?
WE'RE TELLING YOU THAT NOW
IS NOT A GOOD TIME FOR THIS,
OKAY?!
Ah! Lysander!
Oh, Master Keiichi...
Your bath is ready, sir...
And the water is just right.
Good... Well, I guess
I'll go on in.
Would you like me to wash
your back for you, my liege?
More importantly, how is
my dinner coming along?
It is being prepared
as we speak, sir.
Then I suppose you may join me,
once you've finished with that.
Very good, sir.
Splish splash splish...
Ahh...!
♪ Oh, fishy fishy fish... ♪
--This feels great!
♪ Herring and tuna. ♪
♪ Oh, fishy fishy fish... ♪
If you'll permit me... I will
now wash your back for you.
Ah... this sure
feels like heaven!
This evening's main course...
...is a Scandinavian delicacy
known as surstromming.
Oh, boy! It smells great!
Hey, thanks for the meal!
Mm...! This is delicious!
It is a great
honor to hear that.
Ah, yes! Why don't
you have some, too?
It would be wasted on me, sir.
Oh, don't be modest.
Come a little closer!
Well, if you won't
come willingly,
I guess I'll just have to--
Ack!
[stomach growls]
Grr! I'm such an idiot!
I'm so sorry...!
I thought it might help,
but our pretending just
made you even hungrier
than you were before, didn't it?
No, that's not the
problem at all... I swear!
Hm?
Wait a minute...
The space is infinite
above and around,
but the floor feels
pretty solid...
I've got it!
The space is infinite
both out and up,
but it isn't "infinitely" DEEP!
In other words, the
space beneath the floor
might actually be normal!
Right...! This might be
the way out of here!
Keiichi, please wait!
Huh?
What happens if you're
wrong about this?
If we make a tear
in this dimension...
it might go through
to another world!
Yeah, but...
Ah...
Let's open it.
Huh?!
I think I'd rather
take my chances
and fall into an unknown world
than be stuck in this
infinite dimension forever.
I guess you're right.
Besides... it doesn't
matter where we end up...
...as long as I've
got you with me.
Mm...
Ah...
One, and a two, and a... THREE!
Huh?!
AAAHH! It is another world!
You've done it, Keiichi!
Lysander! Where did you go?!
Meow...
Ah! Lysander!
Oh, thank goodness
you're all right!
Well, it looks like Morisato's
not around, so I guess for today
you'll just have to put up with
the other cat food I bought.
Huh? Hey, wait a minute.
Isn't that Chihiro?
That must've been
her cat we found
when we crossed over
from the other dimension.
What if you make six machines
that shorten time by a day each?
Well, I suppose I could make
those in only half a day.
So that would take me
only three days total!
Oh, jeez... You know, I think
it's peaceful enough out here.
Keiichi... I guess I do want
to remain a goddess after all.
I'm only going to have to be
without my license for a week.
But... I was wondering...
if it would be all right
if I still stay with you...
even if I can't use
any of my powers?
Well, of course! You can stay
here for as long as you want!
But... Keiichi?
Huh?
Being human isn't so bad either.
My goddess powers are causing
Keiichi great misfortune.
What can I possibly do to help
her during her greatest test?
Next time: "Ah! Would it
be okay if I were a demon"
Even if... you
weren't a goddess...