You almost had them, Mara.
But, as always, you managed
to blow it at the end.
Now then... where do you
think we should go from here?
Insolent fool!
Do you not see my head?!
Your head?
Are you the Renegade Priest?!
Aw, who gives a damn?!
Get 'im, boys!
♪ Aaaaah. ♪
I'll punish you on behalf
of the great Buddha!
♪ Aaaaah. ♪
Oh! Such beautiful singing.
It just washes over my heart!
All right, you guys!
Let's get it on!
Such barbarous behavior...
It's just so uncivilized.
We should place greater
emphasis on love.
Love is somethin' that can only
be truly won through combat!
Why it almost seems as though,
we now have a fourth
sister, doesn't it?
Aw jeez, it was bad enough
when we just had one of her!
Not to mention, it's not
too much fun watching TV
when she keeps switching
back and forth like that.
Hey, do something!
Uh.
Why are you staring at me with
such a funny look on your face.
Um, come fix this TV.
Uh, Sk... Sku... Tiny.
HEY! WHO ARE YOU CALLIN' TINY?!
And why are you
sounding out my name
like you can't remember it?!
Sku... Your name's
Skuld...! Yeah.
Um...? What's wrong with you?
Uh, nothing - it's nothing!
Hey, wasn't Mara supposed to dig
up some information about that
"heretical pot" she used on Urd?
Hey, Belldandy?
AAAAAHHH!
Whatever that was, it sure
didn't sound too good.
I guess I must've forgot to
turn on Banpei's safety switch.
Uhhhh...
Well, I have to say,
that totally sucked!
Hey! This was all your
fault to begin with,
so stop crying about it!
So, did you manage to
find any information?
Well, that pot got mixed up in
a mail order that I had placed,
so the original sender and its
origin are both unknown.
Therefore, trying to track it
didn't get me anywhere...
What were you thinking using
such a questionable item
in the first place?!
Now, just hang on a minute!
It's not like I haven't given
this any thought after all.
Oh yeah?
Then where'd it come from?
Regardless of its origin...
that heretical pot
is without a doubt
an item of legendary proportion.
Frankly speaking, it's not
something a First Class goddess
or demon would be
able to master.
However, if we were
talking about someone
even more powerful than that...
Wait a minute.
Are you trying to say that...
Someone more powerful
than we are...
In other words,
the Almighty One.
Or... possibly even the...
ruler of demonkind...
So who is this
ruler of demonkind?
Don't you dare take the
name of our ruler in vain,
you insolent human!
The ruler of demonkind
is the ultimate authority
over all demons.
It's our equivalent of
heaven's Almighty One!
Oh, Urd...
Tr... Trou-ba...
My, my! I'm surprised to see
you out here all by yourself.
Who are you again?
WHAT?!
Well, I see you're still
your old, sarcastic self.
You may have
beaten me last year,
but there's no way it's going
to happen again this year.
You remember that!
Ah... I really admire how
energetic and full of
vitality that Sayoko is.
Ah! SAYOKO, that's right!
She's Sayoko!
Now that I think about it,
she really was a lot of fun
to toy with, wasn't she?
Oh, well if it isn't Urd!
So, what brings you here today?
Uh, I, um...
Oh! I just happened
to be passing by...
Mr. Tamiya, Mr. Otaki.
Mr. Tamiya?!
M-M-Mr. Otaki?!
I'll go get a doctor right away!
Huh?
Just take it easy,
we'll be right back!
I guess I have some pretty
good friends, don't I?
Yeah... You sure do.
It was a sunset just like this
when I was here with that boy...
Don't tell me that you've
forgotten about Shohei as well?
Oh, you're right! That's it.
His name was Shohei!
Well, I guess it's about time...
I'll count on you to
take care of the rest.
Are you sure you're
okay with this?
Your soul is being
drawn steadily closer
towards the divine.
At this rate...
My demonic half will disappear.
And when the demonic
side is gone,
a new goddess will
be born in its place.
Sure sounds great, doesn't it?
Great?! To abandon
all the memories
of the days we spent as
a hybrid goddess/demon...
All the people we met...
and the bonds we've made?
Well, it's just...
Tell me the truth...
You're scared, right...?
Of losing all these memories...
And especially of
losing that special bond
that you carry with...
that person.
Kinda funny to say
this to myself,
but you have a
lousy personality.
But I AM you. Remember?
Is that true?!
At this rate, I'm afraid
that the demonic side of Urd
will disappear completely.
No way!
What exactly what makes
you so sure about that?
Don't you remember...
what Urd was like earlier?
What she was like?
Uh!
Yes... the memories of her
demonic side are disappearing.
So I guess that means
Urd will eventually become
one hundred percent
goddess, doesn't it?
Not really such a bad thing,
when you think about it...
Well, yes, but...
It just means the end of some
dumb goddess, who'd actually
hang out with mean-spirited,
capricious demons.
I really don't see what
all the fuss is about!
Stop that!
I don't want that to happen!
If Urd really does
become like Big Sis,
then I won't have
anyone to fight with.
We can't let that happen!
Are you sure there isn't
anything we can do for her?
Maybe we can ask
the Almighty for help,
like you were saying earlier?
Mm-mm... I afraid
that wouldn't work.
The Almighty One could probably
restore Urd's personality.
Maybe even back to its
original state from before...
But then...
It's more likely the Almighty
One would take this opportunity
to rewrite Urd's programming
and make her a full-fledged
goddess instead.
So I guess it's hopeless, huh?
I can't believe you guys
have already forgotten
what I was telling you earlier!
Huh?
But I'm honestly a little
reluctant to say it though.
I'm afraid that's
the only option left.
You came back!
You see, it's like Mara said...
There's only one person...
who has power equal
to the Almighty...
and might be willing to
work out some kind of deal,
depending on how
we approach her...
You're right.
She could probably do it.
Who is "She"?
The ruler of demonkind...
...named Hild.
Well, it would appear that
we've found our answer...
My demonic half says that
she doesn't want to forget...
...her memories as a
half-goddess, half-demon,
and especially not
that certain someone...
I really feel I should do what
I can to respect her wishes.
I suppose that makes
me a terrible goddess?
No, Urd.
Well, then I'll just
leave the rest to you.
If I stay concealed, it will
temporarily halt the progression
towards full divinity.
Thanks for everything,
my other half.
Well, I'll go call her.
Right!
So is it really
that easy to just
pick up the phone and call her?
How should I know?!
What are you guys acting
so freaked out for anyway?
Hey! Just shut up...!
You should consider
yourself lucky
that you don't have to know.
Uh! Hello?
Mm-hm... it has been a while.
Well, this is probably the first
time I've ever called you.
An old friend of hers?
No, I don't think it's quite
like that... You see...
Huh?
You must know about
what's happened, right?
Come on, don't play dumb.
I KNOW you know!
Huh? Wha...?!
Wait just a minute!
But we're not ready to...
Hello?! Hello?! Uh!
What happened?
She said she's coming over.
--Huh?!
--What...?!
The ruler of demonkind
is coming here now?!
That's right.
What would you expect,
she IS my mother, after all.
Amazing...
She's here.
You mean that
she's... Urd's mother?
Huh...?
Oh, Urdie!
It's been far too long!
Couldn't you have at
least tried to arrive
a little more quietly?
Oh, but I was holding back
my power as much as I could!
After all, I'd normally blow
a little town like this away
without even breaking a sweat!
Is she really all that powerful?
Yes. All the jewelry she
wearing on her hair and arms
are probably to
seal her powers.
What?!
If that's indeed the case,
then her true power must be--
So you're Belldandy?
And that means
you must be Skuld?
Yes...
You two look just like him!
Hild is... Urd's mother...
Is she really the
ruler of all demonkind?
It's very nice to
meet you, Miss Hild.
And I suppose
you're Keiichi Morisato?
She's just like Urd...
She doesn't seem to listen
to anything you're saying.
Ah, c'mon. I'm not that bad.
I have to admit, I really
like guys like you.
Now, tell me, Keiichi...
what kind of desires
lie behind those unassuming
eyes of yours, huh?
I would just love to find out.
So... How 'bout you
tell me the whole story
as to why I've come here?
Oh, and no trying to run
away now, my dear Mara.
Perish the thought, Lady Hild!
I would never dream of
doing something like that.
Hmm...
Fusing a goddess
and a demon, huh?
Though it's true there's
nothing I can't do,
it would be a pain.
And this does seem like a good
opportunity to choose just one.
I have no such intentions.
I am half-goddess, half-demon.
And anything other than that
just wouldn't be me anymore.
I don't mind returning
you to how you were,
but what if I had you
come back with me
to the demon realm
once I've done it?
Huh?!
I thought you'd say that.
Even if I am half demonic,
I'm still a goddess
and therefore belong here.
You see, it's something I take
a great deal of pride in.
And so I cannot agree
to that condition...
no matter what.
Hm...
Hey! Do you really
think you're in a position
to set terms
around here?
That weird doo-dad
from the demon realm
caused this whole mess
in the first place!
You're the one who's...
...to blame?
Ah!
Even if that artifact
were somehow
related to the demon realm,
why should it bother you?
With the sole exception
of killing each other,
anything goes in the battle
between gods and demons.
Meaning that I then bear
absolutely no responsibility
in this matter.
One could argue that you're
in fact the one to be blame
for this situation,
having fused Urd back together
using that poorly
built contraption...
But since it was my dearest
daughter making the request,
I thought maybe
I'd help her...
with a few minor conditions.
Would you mind easing up
a bit on my little sister?
Just what I'd expect from
the ruler of demonkind--
she can strike fear in one's
heart with a single glance.
Okay, let's do this...
We'll just forget about
Urd coming back with me.
But as an alternative...
It seems to me that
it would be only fair
if you were to grant me
one little wish, Urdie.
What kind of wish
did you have in mind?
--That's-a-secret.
--Mm!
But then if you just decide
to tell her to go with you,
she won't be able to refuse!
Ahh!
Not too shabby...
But that's really all
you've got, now isn't it?
Would you care to
try again, Hild?
That's all right.
I think I'll pass.
Huh?!
I'd hate to make you have
to overexert yourself.
Well, then...
Keiichi...
I'm afraid we can't have you
underestimating us demons,
now can we?
So this will have to be
a formal contract...
and we demons make very certain
we honor all our contracts.
So... you're saying that trust
is essential in doing business?
Exactly...! Oh, I just
love intelligent men!
We demons will gladly
accept anyone's wish,
so long as we're
compensated in full.
If one were to desire the
destruction of this world...
Well, even that's not
out of the question.
No way!
Of course, the wishes we
grant are in direct proportion
to what's offered in return,
so I think that
might be a bit much.
But as long as something
is given in return,
we'd do it any time.
Went off on a tangent
there, didn't I?
So, Urdie, what
do you want to do?
Okay. As long as whatever
this wish of yours is
doesn't damage my
pride as a goddess.
Oh! I assure you it won't!
I swear in the name
of the Almighty.
That makes it even
more untrustworthy!
Do you really think
we can trust her?
I think it will be fine.
Demons, like goddesses, take
contracts very seriously.
And besides...
Besides what?
Oh, Bell dear.
Hm?
Would you come
over here for a sec?
Coming!
What is it, Hild?
That Keiichi's
quite a guy, isn't he?
There aren't too many
who can stand up
to the ruler of demonkind
and say how they truly feel!
If you don't mind...
would you give him over to me?
No, I won't.
Well now, you're more
straightforward than you look,
aren't you?
I was wondering if I might
ask you a question, Miss Hild?
Lemme guess...
About why he and I split up?
Not that.
I was curious as to why you were
waiting for Urd to call you.
It's not like I was
waiting exactly.
I see. Well, if that's the case,
then I guess that's
all right too.
You really are just
like him, Belldandy.
Just like that part I
always hated about him.
Well... don't go worrying
yourself over it
because I'm only doing
what's best for Urdie and me.
Do you really think so?
Yes, I do.
Hey Urd, so what's the deal?
Do you like totally
hate your mother?
Well, it's not exactly a matter
of whether I love
or hate her...
All righty then...
Shall we begin?
Hm!
I hate to admit it, but she is
quite a sight to behold.
Raising such an
incredible field of magic
in just the blink of an eye...
C'mon! Don't go gushing over
a little old thing like that!
After all, you're the
one who'll be doing
all the rest of the
work from here on out.
What "work" is that?
You think I'm
going to chant
all five hundred twelve
verses on my own?
You're gonna have to help me
out with all the divine parts!
Wait a minute!
Don't tell me that you
don't know how to do it!
Daughter of the one and
only ruler of demonkind...
and you can't even help out
with the divine part
of the circle!
Oh dear Almighty...
All right, fine. I'll do it!
Just cut that out, will you?
Huh?
Skuld?
Belldandy, you too?
We're going to help you get
through this, Urd. Don't worry.
You guys are the best.
Okay, let's give it a shot.
♪ Aaahh... ♪
Good, good, it's working.
Damn! I can't keep up
with this divine part!
♪ Aaahh... ♪
I guess this was
worth doing after all.
♪ Aaahh... ♪
I'm finally back
to my true self.
Now then...
Uh?
Since I've kept up my end,
are you ready to hear my wish?
All right, go ahead.
I want you to
call me "Mom"!
Forget it.
Fine, then I'm
changing you back!
Oh Urd, you do
understand, don't you?
How Hild really feels about you?
Yeah, I think I have a pretty
good idea about that.
But, then, don't you--
No way.
That is exactly the reason why
I can't have any
love for my mother.
But Urd!
If I were to love her...
...my soul would be pulled
over to its demonic side.
And since allowing
that to happen
would conflict with my
pride as a goddess...
There's no way I'll say it!
--All right.
--Ah!
We'll just say the favor
was on me this time.
You silly girl...
It's a shame you had to take
after me in that regard.
Mm...
Oh, Moth...
...eaten old hag.
It seems like I did a lousy job
bringing you up, didn't I?!
You're forgetting that you
didn't bring me up at all!
Remember, darling, now
that you owe me one...
I will be back
one day to collect.
I don't recall
owing you anything.
Right... Well, we'll just see
about that, dearest daughter.
Don't worry. I'll be seeing
you again, my little Urdie.
Hopefully, not for
a very long time.
You goddesses are
ruining with my plan
to increase our demonic share!
So she decides to set them up
with an old-fashioned lamp.
But what kind of powers
could it have?
Next time, "Ah! Do Demons
Have Any Dignity?"
Oh, how cute!
Your wish is my command!