It will... It won't.
Will... It won't.
A phone call most
definitely will... come!
But it's taking too long!
I've had it!
I can't take it anymore!
When?! When am I ever
going to get a phone call?!
How is it possible that I,
the Earth Help Center's
Number One goddess,
with my magnificent skills,
could not have any clients?
And yet...
This frustration will just make
me all the more enthusiastic
when I do.
Step right up...!
For I shall happily grant
your each and every wish!
Ah...
Is it too cold for you
to sit out here...?
Perhaps we should
go back inside?
Uh... No, I'm okay, thanks.
Anyhow... Take a look.
Hm...
Oh!
They turned out so nicely.
I didn't think they'd
make her this happy.
I guess I have you to
thank for this, too, Megumi.
What's with you two?
You've been holding
hands all day.
Oh... Well, it's just that...
Hey, I thought you were busy.
What brings you
over here, Megumi?
This.
That's what... brought you?
Mm-hm... Actually, I just
bought myself a new one...
so I thought if I passed
this one along to you, Kei...
I can't afford to buy it.
If I recall, you don't
have a camera, do you, Kei?
So what if I don't have one?
Well, here we are with New
Year's right around the corner,
and you won't have any
pictures of your girlfriend
decked out in her kimono.
I don't think that's something
YOU need to be worrying about!
Maybe not, but I'm positive
that you'll miss not having
a single memorable picture
of the two of you together!
I'm just saying...
that a camera is a must-have
for a couple in love!
Uh...
So... whaddya say?
Eh?
Uh...
Right. I'm going to take one!
Jeez... Talk about a little
sister who really "cares"
about her big brother!
But that three hundred bucks
wasn't so easy to part with...
--Um, Keiichi?
--Hm?
Did you see this?
Ah! I'll bet Urd
took this picture...
But when did she get
a hold... of the camera?
Pictures are so nice,
aren't they?
When you sit here
looking at them like this,
it's more than memories...
you can actually feel the
warmth from those times as well.
Well, in any case,
what happened that time
sure was crazy, wasn't it?
Hasegawa did return to normal
size the very next morning,
but our hands were still stuck
and wouldn't come apart.
Well, at least we were
able to get them separated
the day after that.
Boy, if they hadn't
come apart then,
I can't even imagine what
Skuld might have done to me.
I'm sure the reason our
hands wouldn't separate...
is because I had no
desire to let go of you.
I really... didn't either...
It's funny, isn't it? This is
all it takes to connect us.
The time has finally
come for you to test
the sharpness of my incredible
space-time-cutting chainsaw
affectionately called
"Texas Murder"!
I... think I get the idea
without the tests.
Oh, did you bring
that to help me out
with the gardening, Skuld?
Uh, I... don't think that's
what she's getting at...
All right, have you said
your prayers, Keiichi?!
Aaahh!
W-Wait a minute, Skuld!
Give all the excuses
you want in hell!
I think you may be
overdoing it just a bit.
Uh?
Urd!
Aaah! Look what you've
done to Texas Murder!
Honestly...
Poor Texas Murder!
Wow! These turned
out pretty nice.
Well, it's only because
I had a great model.
No, it's because you're
a great photographer!
Aw, gee...
My poor little Murder!
That's not exactly
what I meant by that.
Hey...! I just realized!
We oughta show these
awesome photos to Megumi!
Lemme see, I think
Megumi's number is...
Ah, hello...? Hey, it's me.
Well, hello there!
Thank you for calling.
You have reached
the Earth Help Center!
Eh?
It's your lucky day!
You have just been approved
to receive personal
assistance from a goddess.
Now, kindly wait one moment
and I shall be there shortly to
discuss your individual needs!
So pleased to meet you!
I am here from...
the Earth Help Center...
Goddess First Class...
Second Category...
Unlimited License.
I am the goddess...
Peorth, at your service!
This can't be happening.
I actually called ANOTHER one?
It's been so long
since my last client,
I can't wait to get started!
I should strike a pose!
Maybe this would be better...
Perhaps I would look even sexier
in this position, like so...
I shall grant you whatever
it is your heart desires!
Come on, just tell me which pose
you think is best here, okay?!
Excuse me...
Have you by any chance come here
so you can grant me a wish?
Oh, yes, yes, yes, YES!
That's correct!
I heard the cries of your heart
and have descended from
Heaven to fulfill your wish!
It's true! I shall
grant the wish
that is harbored deep
within your heart!
As it happens, I'm
pretty much covered
in the goddess
department already...
Huh?
Hey, Keiichi! If you're
on the phone with Megumi,
then remind her to bring over
the Great Space War video, okay?
Huh?!
Oh, and by the way...
Urd?!
Peorth?!
What in the name of heaven
are you doing here?!
I might ask the
same question of you!
Hey, Keiichi, would
you please tell Megumi
I need her to bring back
the galactic soldering iron
I lent her the other...
Huh?
PEORTH?!
Skuld's here, too?!
But-how-could-this-be...?!
Why are there already
TWO goddesses here?
What the hell is going on
in this place, huh?!
Well... actually...
Oh, Keiichi?
Do you suppose we ought to
make some reprints for Megumi?
Belldandy?!
Ah...! Peorth, it's you!
It's been so long...!
What brings you here like this?
What's the matter?
Would you mind dropping
the act, please?
Or perhaps maybe
you've forgotten
that your organization and
mine are bitter rivals.
Peorth, please.
It's been so long since
we've seen each other.
Regardless...
I'm only here because
he summoned me.
What?! Keiichi called her?
No, it couldn't be!
No, Belldandy, the thing is...
the phone connected me
to Heaven all by itself!
Hm! Now I get it.
Well, no matter.
All else aside, my job is
simply to grant his wish.
All right then...
let's hear your wish!
I shall grant you just one,
which can be anything you like.
Hm...
--No.
--Oh, come on now!
I know what you
really want deep down!
Hm...
How about I just ask you
to go back up to heaven?
Secret technique.
Storm... of Roses!
Waaaahh! Ow! They're prickly!
I'm afraid I cannot tolerate
being made a fool...
And I certainly didn't
come all the way down here
to grant you such
an absurd wish.
This must be awfully
hard on you...
stuck with such an
indecisive client...
Well... At this rate,
I guess you won't be able
to return to Heaven
anytime soon, huh?
Oh, no.
Hm?
You see, I already have
a contract... with Keiichi.
What did you say?!
Then why haven't you
returned to Heaven?
Surely your contract must've
been fulfilled by now, right?
You see, it's all
because of this
really unreasonable
wish that I made.
Unreasonable wish?
"I'd like for a goddess like you
to stay by my side forever"?!
You've gotta be kidding!
It's too much! It's so
funny I'm tossing flowers!
It's unbelievable!
She's seems to be getting
quite a kick out of this.
She's laughing at you,
Keiichi, if you didn't know.
Would you please shut up...
Hold on.
You can not be serious.
I'm sure that the
contract is registered
in Yggdrasil's system.
Why don't you try
doing a search for it?
So, it appears Keiichi's wish
really was registered in there.
The current situation
means it's going to end up
becoming a double contract.
Then that means our
contract is invalid?!
No, it's not.
As a matter of fact,
there aren't any regulations
regarding double contracts...
Because the odds of anyone
placing two such calls
are absolutely
astronomical to begin with.
Besides... a First Class deity
simply does not return
to Heaven empty-handed...
Not after being summoned
to earth to grant a wish.
But I told you,
I don't HAVE any wishes!
Nonsense. You are
simply not aware
of your own deep
desires at present.
Therefore, I am
not going back now.
Not until you have
told me your real wish.
And what the heck is
that supposed to be...?
Listen, Belldandy...
I don't want you to worry...
I'm sure I'll think up
some reasonable wish
and then she can
return to Heaven.
Oh... I'm not
concerned about that...
I'm sure it's going to be okay.
My, my...
It would seem that
Fate has led us both
to the same client, Belldandy.
But I'm sure I heard it... a
suppressed desire of the flesh.
And I'll do... whatever it
takes to grant... that wish...
This one is no good either...
"Please compile the results
of the experiment."
I guess I can't ask her for
help on that kind of stuff...
"Please turn this radio/cassette
player into a CD player!"
But I don't even have any CDs...
"Please let Rossi win the
Championship again this year!"
But that'd probably
make her angry...
I know...! How about "please
bring back the Betamax format!"
Damn... are these lame wishes
honestly the only ones
that I can come up with?
Keiichi's wish...
I'm making too much of this.
It'll be all right.
Keiichi!
Your dinner's ready!
Uh... I'll be right there!
Ah...
I guess this basically
means that I'm not unhappy
with the way my life
is going right now.
Oh, is that right?
The funny thing is, it doesn't
appear that way to ME at all...
I'm telling you it is that way!
Well, in any case, I'm very
sorry to have kept you waiting.
Please follow me.
Who the heck... is gonna
eat all this stuff?!
I have lovingly prepared
all of this just for you.
I'm sorry. But there's no
way I can eat this, Peorth.
You see, Belldandy's already
got dinner ready for me...
No. You are going to
be eating this meal!
After all...
They do... want to be...
eaten by you so very badly!
So... please eat up...
and don't feel like
you need to be timid!
Aaahh!
I am so incredible!
That's the kind of technique
only a First-class
goddess could manage.
What are you doing?
Huh?! Urd?!
What do you want?!
Can't you see I'm trying to
fulfill the divine obligation
that Belldandy has
apparently shirked!
Well, it looks to me rather like
you were torturing the poor man.
Ah...
Thanks for the meal.
It was delicious...
There! Did you see how
delighted Keiichi was just now?!
Listen.
I don't think what you're doing
is going to have any effect.
Oh? And what do you
mean by that, pray tell?
Have a look.
Ah... Is this picture
supposed to mean something?
It's a nice shot, isn't it?
Are you just showing off
your younger sister or what?
That's not the point!
Belldandy's smile looks really
pure and honest, doesn't it?
Uh...
There aren't many
people who could make
a First-class
goddess that happy.
What does that have to do--
Look.
See.
--Oh, is that right?
--Uh?!
Nekomi Park sure is
a nice, big place.
I do hope we'll
have good weather.
I'm certain everything
will be just fine
as long as you're there with me.
You mean, as long
as you are with me!
Thanks again for the meal!
No way... After he ate all
that food just a minute ago?
That's just the kind
of guy that Keiichi is.
No matter how stuffed he is,
if Belldandy has
made food for him,
he can eat however
much is there.
In a way, he's
the ultimate softy.
But then... it's because
Keiichi is like that...
that Belldandy readily
puts so much faith in him.
That's why nothing you do could
possibly make any difference...
as far as their
relationship is concerned...
Well now, I suppose
I'd better go
whip up some indigestion
medicine for Keiichi.
They have faith in each other?
I refuse to believe it!
Belldandy has not
fulfilled her obligation!
That is the only reason I
could have possibly received
a phone call from him!
And so...
By no means will
I ever be defeated
by the likes of Belldandy!
I give up... I've gotta
think of a wish quick.
I've gotta get her off my back.
--Oh, Keiichi.
--Huh?
Why don't you let me
wash your back for you?
Whoa, Belldandy!
What are you doing here?
You sure are being quite
forward today, huh?
If this has anything
to do with Peorth,
I've already thought of my wish!
AAAHH!
I was thinking it
would be really cool
if she could turn this bath into
a hot spring. Pretty cool, huh?
WAAAHHH!
Don't lie to me now, understand?
Surely that isn't what you
REALLY want, now is it?
What the heck are you
doing in my bathroom?!
Well that should be
perfectly obvious!
I came in here to wash
your back for you.
So please allow me
to provide you with
the impeccable service that
Belldandy could never offer you.
She doesn't provide
"services" like that!
You needn't be so shy, Keiichi.
I shall now give you a lesson
on what a First Class
goddess's techniques are like.
And it'll be up
close and personal.
Waah! Cut it out!
C'mon now! There's nothing
to be embarrassed about!
--Sorry!
--Oh!
I will see to it--
that no matter what--
I will be the one to grant
him that wish... not Belldandy!
It's over... I just
can't think of anything.
But that did feel
kinda nice back there...
If only it had been Belldandy...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What is it this time?
I shall transform your
dull clothing into something
that's certain to
stir women's hearts
and drive them absolutely wild!
I'd rather that you didn't.
Here we go!
Ah! A lovely pink
silk nightgown!
Wearing this stunner
tonight is guaranteed
to make Keiichi a
love hunter for sure!
I'm begging you, please
change me back to normal!
Even though it
looks so delicious?
Just put me back
to the way I was!
What the heck does
she mean, "love hunter"?
If Peorth's really going
to be that persistent,
it's only going to make
me afraid of asking her
for any kind of wish at all...
On the other hand, if things
keep going on like this...
it's only going to be
a burden on Belldandy...
Well... time to call it a day.
I've got a bad
feeling about this!
He's a formidable opponent...
to have withstood all
my advances so far...
But... this time
will be different.
I will bring this
to a decisive end.
Come quickly, Keiichi.
I shall indulge you in
my true "customer service."
Now I have... no choice...
I think I'm gonna go take cover.
Belldandy? Belldandy?
Oh, Keiichi...! What are you
doing up at this hour?
Are you having trouble sleeping?
Well, Peorth has completely
taken over my room,
so I can't go in there.
Do you mind if I stay in here
with you for a little while?
Oh, no! Leave it to me.
I'll get her out of there!
No, that's all right.
It looks like she's
already fallen asleep.
I definitely can't let
her see Peorth like THAT.
Well, if she's
already fallen asleep,
why don't I make
you some black tea?
Thanks.
So have you... decided on the
wish you'd like Peorth to grant?
No... I'm having a pretty
rough time with that...
At first, I thought
maybe I'd have her
make this place
into a mansion...
but then I realized
that I actually like it
just the way it is.
Thinking up wishes
is really tough.
I was wondering if...
you thought the wish
you asked me for...
was really the right
one to ask after all?
Well, what made you ask
that, all of a sudden?
You being here right now...
seems to show that I made
right wish, doesn't it?
It may have seemed
like a joke back then...
but at the time it was the only
wish that came into my mind.
I really did feel that way.
From the bottom of my heart...
Oh, Keiichi...
So, you see, my wish has
already been granted.
Yes.
It's all right.
'Cause I wouldn't have made...
that wish to anyone... but you.
Thank you, Keiichi.
Peorth...
Go on, you can come at
me from any direction!
Hic!
What's taking him
so long anyway?
Each of them has a genuine
desire to grant wishes.
But, in trying to accomplish
this by any means possible,
her feelings begin to waver.
Next time, "Ah!
I Want to be of Use to You".
Please, I'm begging you
to stop going overboard!