Thanks for the meal!
Sure... I hope you enjoy it!
Wow, this grilled
yellowtail is delicious!
Do you really think so?
That's wonderful...
I had hoped you would
really like it, Keiichi!
Of course I like it!
I mean, the food you make always
tastes fantastic, Belldandy!
Well, thank you very much.
I'm not just saying
that to flatter you.
--It really is delicious!
--It's okay, I believe you.
There they go again...
Even the miso broth is great!
I mean, it seems as if you
always know exactly what dishes
I like the most somehow...
Keiichi!
The food I've prepared is most
certainly superior to hers!
Here, open your mouth...
it's delicious!
Hey, it's good!
Well, of course it is, silly!
Uh...? Uh!
Say... "ah"!
Isn't that yummy?
And I'm sure it
tastes even better
when I feed it to
you, now doesn't it?
Uh... Huh?
So, does it taste good?
Uh...
Open wide!
You can try...
Peorth...!
You've been reading my issues of
Dobon again, haven't you...?!
Huh?
What do you want?
You perverts!
Skuld! This it's
not what you think!
Keiichi! What is
that supposed to mean?
Come on now, open wide!
Please! Just cut it out, Peorth!
Come on Keiichi... say "ah"!
This is all your fault
for being spineless!
What...?
Don't give me that
lame "what" routine.
Huh...
Keiichi...
Don't tell me that you
actually enjoy having
Peorth all over you?
That's not what
I'm saying at all!
Well then... Why don't you
just send her home already?
Don't you care about
Belldandy's feelings?!
Huh?!
What do you mean?
Of course I do.
Have you already forgotten...
about the wrath of
her "jealousy storm"?
If you keep this behavior up,
she might explode again...
Now... Is that what
you really want?
Uh...
So what's next...?
It's all up to you now.
Excuse me... I'll be right back.
Go right ahead.
What a piece of work...
Oh, no...
Oh yeah, a jealousy storm
is brewing, all right.
That's it!
Even if it might
be a little late...
What we need to do is
organize a fun party
to welcome Peorth so
she feels more at home!
I'll get things
ready right away!
What the...?
So that's what she
was upset about?
Hey, it's good!
Well, of course it is, silly!
Say... "ah."
Oh, now I get it...
That's what I did
wrong the other day!
All right then, I won't
make the same mistake twice!
Next time I'll be sure
to get it right, and--
Hold on! What's this
supposed to mean--
"to be continued next month"?!
But I don't wanna wait!
I wanna know what
happens right now!
You see, the reason I was
ultimately able to find
the bug back then is because
it had gotten inside you.
That's why that job
truly was a joint effort
between the two of us!
Belldandy... You...
Peorth.
Huh? That's a rather
grave expression...
Is something the matter?
Is it about your wish?
Please answer me...
Can you just tell me what
you want me to wish for?
My, that's a strange
thing to ask.
Shouldn't a wish be something
that you, yourself,
personally desire?
Well, it should be,
but I just...
To begin with, a wish
can only be entered into
Yggdrasil's systems when spoken
by the recipient of that wish.
Sadly, my own desires in this
matter are entirely immaterial.
You're probably right.
Nevertheless...
We won't get anywhere at
this rate, now will we?
I suppose I'd better
give you a little hint.
What's the hint?
I want you to go into your
bedroom, and take a look
at what's inside your
middle desk drawer, okay?
My middle desk drawer?
What is she talking about?
But... this is a...
Peorth!
Did you find it already?
Yeah...
What kind of "hint"
is this supposed to be?!
Ah, yes... that's it all right.
Would you just tell me what the
heck this is supposed to mean?!
It means that you're going to
have to start being much more
honest with yourself,
that's what it means.
Huh?
It can't be...
Are you saying that the
reason you've come here
is to fulfill my "desires"?
You mean to say you didn't
figure that out 'til just now?
Well... never you mind...
As long as you understand
how everything works now...
So! Go right ahead and
lay that big wish on me!
No way.
What the heck is that
supposed to mean?!
Forget it.
I'm not interested in anything
that doesn't involve love...
You mean you're
really not interested
if love isn't part
of the equation?
Right...
You're saying you don't have
any love for me, aren't you?
Well, isn't it obvious?
Very well then. If you insist
on putting it like that...
Huh?
Keiichi... I am so very
deeply in love with you.
So, tell me...
did that help at all?
Peorth, what are
you talking about?!
Huh?
I remember Belldandy saying that
goddesses aren't supposed to
have the ability to tell lies.
I think Urd and Skuld can,
since they're Second
Class goddesses...
but there should be any way that
a First Class goddess like you
would be able to do that!
Please just tell me
what's going on?!
You've somehow been under
the wrong impression...
Well... that's
that then, huh...?
Come on now, Keiichi,
let's hear that wish, okay?
Huh?
Well?
All right...
I want you to...
fulfill my every desire...
Is that what...
you want me to say?
Whoa, wait! That's not my wish!
No, that's not it!
Congratulations.
Your wish has been accepted.
Good news, Keiichi...
it was accepted!
Huh?
Now... the time has come for
me to grant you that wish...
Aahhhh!
You're not getting away
from me, Keiichi.
I hope Keiichi finds this meal
as delicious as the last one.
Belldandy...
What's the matter, Keiichi...?
You seem so distracted...
Hey, Big Sis, have you
seen my issues of Dobon?
What is the matter
with you, Keiichi?!
Look, you've got the
wrong idea, Skuld!
We just ran into
each other by mistake!
It was an accident! I swear!
Uh... Huh?
I finally caught you,
Keiichi... Uh!
You're not getting away.
You're the one who took my
issues of Dobon Manga Monthly,
--aren't you?!
--Hm?
I was just getting to the
good part in Miracle Micky!
Damn, that boy certainly
is quick on his feet...!
Ah!
That'll do nicely.
Jolt the earth...
Move ahead, faster
than the wind...!
Hurry onward... as if
soaring through the sky!
GO!
You had better not
underestimate me!
Gimme a break...
Well, we got away from
there pretty darn fast...
but I don't know where
I'm gonna go from here.
--Keiichi?
--Huh?
Did something happen
between you and Peorth?
I mean, there must
be some reason why
you're having to
run away from her.
Oh, it's just that
my wish got kinda...
What about your wish?
Ah...
Did something happen
with your wish?
No way! Absolutely
nothing happened!
Keiichi! Behind us!
What?! No way!
Keiichi...!
There's no point in running.
I will satisfy your passions!
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about!
Oh, Keiichi!
I already told you--
that wasn't my wish!
What's going on?
Uh, I'll explain
it to you later.
Well, in the meantime,
I'll get us away from Peorth.
Gazing intently
upon small stars...
I listen carefully so I
can hear their whispers...
All ye who twinkle unite,
and invite this into
your tiny world.
Aaaahhh!
She won't be able to catch
up to us for a while now.
Well, Belldandy's certainly
outdone herself this time...
Hey, you did it!
Nice job, Belldandy!
Hey! W-What's wrong?
Oh, I'm nearly out of gas.
We have to stop for--
Oh no! I didn't even think
about bringing my wallet.
I guess we'll just have
to pull over... Damn...
That Belldandy...!
I can't believe she'd have
the nerve to interfere!
In fact, that is precisely
what I hate about her so much!
So... what do I do now?
Is this the extent of a
First Class Goddess' powers?
What are you doing here?
In case your wondering...
You'll probably find those
two at the university.
Huh?
But why... Why are you
telling me this, Urd?
Let's just say it's
for Belldandy's sake.
I don't know if
you've caught on,
but even she can be pretty
difficult to deal with.
Don't worry. You've known
her for some time now.
You'll know what to do.
Well... Good luck!
Wait, Urd...
All right then...
Time to go hunting.
So, what are we gonna do now?
--Um, Keiichi...
--Huh?
What was this wish that you
were talking about earlier?
Uh, well you see, it's, uh...
You're going to have to start
being more honest with yourself.
She's right...
If I claim I didn't
want that, I'd be lying.
And I believe it's what
Belldandy wants as well.
It's not as though she's
deliberately avoiding
it or anything.
But there's something that's
making her keep her distance.
Even when there's love...
Or is there not
any love at all?
Keiichi?
Belldandy...
If I... ever wished...
If I ever did...
Is that... really my wish?
Is it?
Uh, Keiichi?
Uh-huh...
I was wondering about Peorth's
cooking. Was it really good?
Hm?
Be honest with me...
You thought her cooking tasted
better than mine, right?
Belldandy...
No, not at all! Your cooking
was incredible. Delicious.
But you...
The only reason
I ate Peorth's food
is because she was
forcing me to...!
It wasn't like I
enjoyed doing that!
It was good though, wasn't it?
Uh... Um, well, yeah...
I understand.
But I'm trying to
say that yours is...
Belldandy?
Just say it already!
Ah...
Don't tell me that...
she's jealous!
She's jealous of Peorth?!
That's what I was
trying to tell you.
No way...
Oh, Keiichi... What am
I supposed to do...?
I just don't know
what I should do.
Belldandy...
I've finally tracked you down!
Why, Peorth...?
Why on earth are you running
Keiichi down like this?!
Running him down?
I'd say you're the one
who's doing that!
Huh?
It would seem
impossible, Belldandy,
but I believe you've
forgotten that Keiichi is a man.
Haven't you?
If you're only here
because it's your duty...
then I feel sorry for Keiichi.
--Peorth!
--Could it be...
You're not aware that you're
still a First Class Goddess?
Just stop this
right now! I won't--
Do you have any idea
why I was summoned
down to Earth
in the first place?
Huh?
Even if it was caused
by a mistake...
I have traveled down here
to the surface world
in order to grant a wish.
I am here to grant your
wish, Keiichi Morisato.
Belldandy...
You were asking
Keiichi whether or not
something had happened earlier
between the two of us.
Well, Keiichi told me his wish.
He said that he wants me
to fulfill his every desire.
Belldandy! It's not true!
Peorth made her report to Heaven
before I could get the chance
to finish talking
to her about it...!
It's all a big mistake!
Belldandy! Please wait!
Belldandy!
Belldandy...
It's not just my duty.
If it were, it wouldn't
hurt so much...
But I...
All right, Keiichi...
--Why don't we get started...?
--Stop it!
I want to...
Come on, Keiichi...
--Cut it out!
--I will grant what you desire.
To tell you...
Belldandy.
It's true that I
might have desired it
somewhere deep in my heart...
And it's even possible
that's the reason
why my phone call went through
to Peorth in the first place.
But then...
That was actually because...
I love you, Belldandy.
And you're the one...
I want to be with forever.
Because of who you are...
Belldandy!
I'm glad...! Because
I love you, Keiichi!
Belldandy...
I really love you!
What are you doing?
Peorth here.
Yes, I've completed my mission,
and I'm ready to return.
Peorth?!
What's gotten into you
all of a sudden?
Y'know, it's a real
shame for you, Keiichi...
You see, I am famous
throughout Heaven
for providing the
very best in services.
Uh... Peorth!
Ah!
Do you mean...
you did all that...
just to get me to
say what I did?
--Belldandy.
--Huh?
So you know, that's something
I do truly detest about you.
But then again, it's
also the reason why
I could never truly hate you.
Ah!
--Oh, Peorth.
--Peorth, wait!
And in case we should
never meet again,
it's been an absolute pleasure
fulfilling your request.
Peorth!
Was this to repay me for the
mistake you made about me?
Was it?
Or is it because...
you really do love Keiichi?
Ahh!
Aaaaahh!
They're gone!
My issues of Dobon Manga
Monthly are all gone!
Ran Ran and Best Friends
and everything else!
Hmm... Oh, no!
What am I going to do about
getting the next volume?
I really did want to
fulfill his wish after all.
Everyone has tried to go back
at least once in their lives.
But a single-minded
passion brings new inspiration
to hearts that are
about to give up.
Next time, "Ah! Catch Your
Dream With Your Own Hands."
Why are seniors so afraid of
the Auto Club's first manager?