I'm finally finished...
Great job!
You've done very well.
Hey Belldandy...
Sorry you have to come to
all my lectures with me.
There's no need to apologize.
I really do enjoy it.
Hm?
Because I learn so many
new things every time.
So I actually look
forward to coming to class.
Do you mean that?
You seem to be having fun, too.
Oh... do you think so?
Yes, I do!
But the reason it's fun
is because I'm with you.
Oh, Keiichi...
Yes, Belldandy...
Aahh!
All right, it's time for some
more fun with the Auto Club!
So let's all give
it our best shot!
For the Nekomi Tech
Auto Club! Oh, yeah!
Why do I have a bad
feeling about this?
If you got a problem with
your car or motorcycle
why don'cha let the
Auto Club handle it?
We are now
providing our expert...
Is the Club completely
broke again, Tamiya?
Yeah, and we gotta put
together a killer machine
in time for next
month's drag race.
C'mon, Morisato. Help us out!
Our rates are twenty to
thirty percent below average!
We'll get the job done...
This approach is driving
customers away...
We're good, we're fast,
and we're cheap!
What more could you ask for?!
Um, Keiichi?
Huh?
All we need to do is find people
who are having trouble, correct?
Well, basically, yeah...
Let me... try.
You'll find someone?
Ah...! Someone's having
trouble over there.
Cool!
So you're saying you
can't open the door
because you lost the key?
Get it open it quick!
My event's gonna
start any minute!
This isn't exactly something the
Auto Club normally handles...
You wanna help people
in trouble, don't you?
It's perfectly okay.
Please leave this
matter to the Auto Club.
Guys, that's a little, uh...
Not bad, eh?
I knew you'd be able to help!
I think maybe we'd
better stick to matters
that actually involve
cars from now on...
All right. Very well then.
Hey. Someone slashed my tire.
I was wondering if--
Ah! It's you guys again!
Unforgivable!
--Let's do it, Dai!
--Right on!
Hey!
There ya go, pal.
Hey, it was no sweat, man...
Now, regarding our fee...
Like hell I'm paying you!
--Stop!
--Why, you...
Wait a minute!
Dammit... he gave me
the slip... Oh well!
I suppose Den can hunt him
down for the money later!
Or maybe we'll just
send young Morisato.
--Well, why not?!
--Huh?
Why not just leave this old
thing on campus, hm?
My car would have us there
in a flash--in style!
Come now, Satoko.
How long are you going to
drive that thing around?
I bought it when I was working
my very first part-time job...
so I'm kind of attached to it...
Look, it's simply
not appropriate
for a person of
your social status.
But it still works.
But, it isn't
working right now.
Come. Stop this silliness
and let me take you home.
But, I...
Say, how about I buy you a new
scooter on the way back, okay?
Huh?!
It's quite all right.
There's no need to thank me.
You see, it's no different
than if I were to go out
and just buy you an outfit.
And if you find
you don't like it,
I'll just buy you another one.
One a day, for three days
or ten--whatever it takes!
I could never let you do that!
Think nothing of it. Now...
I'm telling you,
I really don't--
Geez... you've just got
some worn out spark plugs,
that's all.
This plug I've got's
the wrong number,
but the reach looks like
it's close enough...
What do you think
you're doing?!
I just finished telling her
that I'd buy her a new one!
You know, I have no respect
for people who just
toss out perfectly
good vehicles.
Furthermore, I don't
buy that crap about
money being able to
solve all your problems.
I could fix this kind of stuff
until the cows come home.
Okay! All done!
Aaah...!
Uh...
Uh, let's see if the
engine starts okay...
Ta-da!
That's great!
You take good care of
this thing, don'cha?
What a lucky bike!
Thanks so much for your help!
Aah...!
It's nothin' really.
I'm just doing my job as a--
an active member
of the Auto Club...
so don't worry about
it... See ya!
Please wait...
Well, I'm finally finished...
You've done very well.
Hey Belldandy...
I'm sorry you have to
come to all my lectures.
There's no need to
apologize. It's fun.
Because I get to learn
so many new things here,
I look forward to coming.
Really, you mean that?
Of course I do.
Lucky you...
Man, you got it made...
Otaki?!
Lucky. You're so darn lucky!
So lucky...! So lucky...
Otaki!
Here you go!
Thanks a lot...
Wow, you really did go all out
with the food today, huh?
I'm sorry...!
You said you liked it, so I
guess I got carried away...
Have I made too much?
Uh, no it's fine! I've had
quite an appetite lately...
I'm so glad.
I wish they'd take their
romantic comedy somewhere else.
So lucky...! So darn lucky!
Lucky you, Morisato, lucky you!
Um... Would you like to
have some, too, Otaki?
Please go ahead, if you'd like.
Uh, no thank you.
Huh?! What's the matter...?
You normally just
dig right into it!
You're a lucky guy, Morisato.
To have a girl who'll stay
by your side and all...
I'll have to take you up
on the eats some other time.
Wait, hold on a second, Otaki!
Huh?
Who is it? Door's open, y'know.
Uh... So, what's wrong?
Don't tell me it
stopped working again?!
--Here!
--Huh?!
I made this to thank
you for yesterday...
I hope you enjoy it.
See you later!
Hey, wait! Hold up!
Could that have been
what I think it was?
Yes, I believe he's in
love with her, isn't he?
Huh?!
Y'know, that's what
I think it is, too!
That big furry whose
only interests
are machines and lucky
charms is in LOVE?!
I got it!
Huh?
Satoko Yamano:
Electronics Club member
and First-year Fine Arts major.
Her dad's the
university president.
She's a good student, and
her meek, charming demeanor
has made her popular
among the upperclassmen.
Her measurements are 35-22-32.
Needless to say,
a far cry from my own...
But that doesn't mean...
My measurement are on par
with an eighth-grader's!
Delicious! Absolutely
fantastic, Satoko!
Ah...
Otaki?
Morisato, I've gotta
ask for your advice.
About what?
Uh, never mind! It's cool!
Are you sure?
Look, I said it's cool!
Let fortune smile on you.
Huh?
What the heck was that?
I am certain that your feelings
will come across to her now.
Hm? But, I'm not,
uh... I don't...
Something good awaits
you in that direction!
Something good, huh?
So, you say there's something
good waiting around here?
Look, there it is!
Huh?
You mean this lottery?
That's right.
But do you actually have any
tickets that you can turn in?
--Yeah.
--Huh?!
That's right. I've got some.
I still have 'em from when
I shopped here one time.
All right, you win!
Tickets for two to
the amusement park!
I can't believe I friggin' won!
But what the heck am I gonna
do with these things anyway?
Why don't you invite Satoko
to go along with you?
WHAT?!
Just to pay her back for the
lunch she made you, of course.
Oh okay, I get it!
So you are in love with her,
aren't ya, big guy?
But how do I go about
asking her to come with me?
It'll be fine.
Huh?
What'd we come to
the campus for?
Yeah, and what are we
doing at the Art Studio?
Why don't you go inside now
and try speaking to
Satoko in person?
Ah! There's no way
I can do that!
I'm sure it would show her
how you really feel about her.
Please, you must try to
have greater confidence
in your feelings.
Uh, I'll try...
I, um, uh...
Oh, it's you...
Yeah, hey there.
Um, lovely weather we're
having today, isn't it?
Ah... come on! Just get
to the point already!
The lunch box...
It was delicious!
Thanks a million.
I'm glad to hear that.
Uh... So anyhow,
maybe it's kinda silly,
but to show my thanks,
I was thinking, if you like,
maybe we could, uh...
What the heck?
Huh? I thought it
was right here...
You can do it, Otaki!
Uh...?
What's this?
I... won those in
a lottery downtown,
but I don't have
anyone to go with.
So, like, I don't know if
you'd be up for it or not,
but I was thinking maybe,
if you're not busy,
you'd want to come with me?
That's the place that
just opened, isn't it?
Of course... I would love to!
Really?!
Yes. If it's with you.
Thank goodness...
Kinda hot out today, isn't it?
You think so? I heard it's
supposed to snow tomorrow.
Really? Well, that's funny
cause I'm so hot
I can barely breathe!
Should we go try out
one of the rides then?
All we've done so far
is walk around the park.
Oh, yeah. You're right!
Now let's see...
Oh... brother.
Hey, Keiichi, why
the heck did I have to
come along with you guys, huh?
What do you expect
me to do about it?
He asked all of us
to come with him.
Well, that's easy
enough for you to say.
I mean, you did get to come
with Belldandy, after all.
Morisato!
I don't know what
I'm doing here, man!
Stop stressing out!
Just try to find a fun-looking
ride for right now, okay?
That way seems like
it might be good.
--Huh?!
--Huh?
Head to your left.
Uh...? To the left?
Oh! That's the uh...
Oh, I see...
Do you want to go in there?
Um, well, I didn't really...
It looks like fun!
Huh?!
Meow!
Woof!
Okay, hold still now.
You know, Otaki, I really
do love this sort of thing.
Honestly, Satoko?! Because
I love this stuff, too!
Do you really mean that?!
Arf!
I've got a whole load of these
outfits back at my place.
You think I could
come see them some time?
Woof!
Okay, you two.
Just hold it right there.
They're really getting into it.
Yeah, and it looks like
she's just as much
of a weirdo as he is.
That was so much fun!
Yeah, so what do you
think we oughta do next ?
How about that one over there?
Okay!
So tell me, what kind of
turnout have you been getting?
We've been open two weeks now,
and we're operating at
eighty percent above the
forecast attendance level.
Superb... This is certainly
a fitting new business venture
for the Aoshima
conglomerate... Uh?
Hey! Let's go on
the merry-go-round.
And the tea cups
after that, okay?
Sure! You got it!
What are those two
doing here together?!
Is there something
the matter, sir?
Obviously! Stop the
merry-go-round at once!
Huh?!
I'm sorry.
But we had to close to conduct
some emergency maintenance, sir.
But it was working fine
until just a minute ago!
I'm telling you,
it's an emergency...
It's no big deal, Otaki.
Let's go to the next ride.
All right, Satoko...
You're closed, too?
Sorry, we have to conduct
emergency maintenance.
But doesn't this seem
a little weird to you?
We just need to do
some maintenance!
Don't gimme that crap!
Huh?
Well, there we go,
it's working now!
Just a little trouble
with the electronics.
Hey! What do you
think you're doing?
C'mon, let's go ride it, Satoko.
Sure!
Why is that damn
thing working...?!
Get it shut down
or you're fired!
But I'm positive I sent them
the orders to stop it, sir.
Damn it!
Ya know, I was kinda worried
there for a minute...
It certainly does seem like
someone is trying to
interfere with their date.
Eh?
What the hell kind of
management system...
Toshiyuki?!
Oh, that's right.
This amusement park is part
of the Aoshima Conglomerate.
But why on earth would Toshiyuki
be getting in Otaki's way?
Because, unlike me,
Satoko is loved by everyone.
Huh?
Perhaps we should
go to the university.
Huh?
Is the date over already?
Please tell Otaki that
it might be a good idea
for them to go to
the campus now.
Uh... Sure...
Dai...
You live it up
for me, too, man...
So, you think this
looks all right?
It's totally adorable!
I'm sorry to ask you to
come along to help me
with a project I
had forgotten about.
Ah, it's nothing! I'm glad
to be helping you out!
But you don't have to
single out only one of 'em.
I brought a bunch
along with me...
That's awesome...
It's actually really
inspiring to me.
I'm so glad you're giving
me a hand with this, Otaki!
You really mean it?!
Yes!
Ha ha!
Hey, Satoko...
you don't think that
I'm some kind of weirdo
or anything like that, do you?
No, I don't think that at all.
You've been great, and
if it weren't for you,
I couldn't finish
this project.
Oh, Satoko!
Ah ah! The model's
not supposed to move!
Yes, ma'am!
They seem to be
enjoying themselves.
Well, I guess you could say
our work is done here.
No freakin' way!
I am not going to keep letting
things go so smoothly for them!
Hey Belldandy, I'm sorry you
have to come to all my lectures.
But why are you apologizing,
Keiichi? I really do enjoy it.
Oh... do you really
mean that, Belldandy?
I do. And from
what I can tell,
you seem to be having fun, too.
Really... you think so?
Yes, I really do.
Oh, Belldandy...
Keiichi...
--Morisato!
--AAAHHH!
Satoko invited me
over to her place!
Wow! That's awesome, Otaki!
But I'm not used to doing
this kind of stuff, man!
Well, I'm certainly
not used to it!
But you have been goin'
steady with Belldandy
for a whole year, dude!
First, I think it would be a
good idea to come across
as clean-cut as
you possibly can.
Furthermore, you should behave
like a chivalrous knight,
a perfect gentleman.
Come across as clean-cut
and chivalrous, huh?
You got it, babe!
How about this? Satoko
thought this one was cool!
She said "like" a
chivalrous knight...
Hmph...! Then how about this?!
Hey Otaki.
Why don't you try something
a little more normal?
I really think Satoko would
like something like this more.
Are you positive this
getup will be okay?
Wouldn't the suit of
armor look better?
Listen! I'm telling
you it's fine!
When you arrive, give her this
bouquet of flowers, and say,
"thank you so very much
for inviting me to your home."
Now, do you think you
can remember that?
Thanks, Belldandy!
All right, then... I'm off!
I told you the
armor was no good!
Well, Satoko thinks it's cool!
This really sucks!
At this rate, he'll steal
Satoko away from me...!
What the hell am I going to do?
What are you doing?
Huh?
What on earth are you
doing back there anyway?
That's it! I have
a favor to ask of you!
A favor?
Man... that's one
big-ass house... Mm...
Yamano Residence.
Ah, right!
Thank you so very much for
inviting me to your home!
Um, this bouquet is just a token
I have to offer you, so I...
My, my, how thoughtful of you.
Satoko, you sound like
you might've caught a cold
or something, I... UH!
Ugh, I wonder if
this is gonna work...
Toshiyuki...? And Sayoko, too?!
What're you doing here?
Ah, I've been expecting
you, Sayoko...
Is this the young man you
wanted to introduce to me?
That's right, President Yamano.
President?
Aoshima, Four Wheels
Club president.
Oh, don't tell me--
you mean you didn't know
that Satoko's father is the
president of Nekomi Tech?
Otaki!
Huh?
Satoko!
Oh, is this man here to see you?
Yes, Dad. This is Otaki,
from the Auto Club.
The Auto Club?
It's very nice to meet you.
Yes, the infamous Auto Club.
--Their poor reputation...
--What's that?!
was my reason for creating
the Four Wheels Club.
As a matter of fact,
that's what we're here to
talk to you about today.
Now that Nekomi Tech has
the Four Wheels Club,
don't you think we should
just disband the Auto Club?
What the hell are
you talking about?!
Oh, my. Perhaps we should talk
about its reputation on campus?
But if we take
that into account,
simply disbanding the club
may not be enough...
Otaki...
The situation's starting to
look pretty grim over there.
Don't worry. It'll be all right.
Because Otaki still has plenty
of good fortune surrounding him.
I'll be back in a minute!
Ugh... It smells like
something's burning.
Oh, no! I left the
food on the stove!
Huh?!
--Man, this is bad!
--Get some water!
Grease fire.
Aoshima, have you got a fire
extinguisher in your car?
How the hell should I know?!
Leave it to me to be without
my tools at a time like this!
Quick! Get me that water!
But you said water was no good.
I'll soak my coat and
throw it over the pot.
All we need to do is just
throw some water on there
and be done with it!
--No, don't!
--Shut up!
Aaaah!
Look out!
Satoko!
If this keeps up...
Sleep now, oh spirits of flame!
Let your power slip
into profound silence!
Aaah...!
Oh... the fire's out...
You're not hurt, are you,
Otaki? Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
But, look... your back is...
Oh, I forgot.
Armor.
Thank goodness...
--I like you!
--Hm?
Now that's what I expect
of a Nekomi Tech student!
That's the kind of nerve
and decision-making
a mechanic needs to have!
On the other hand,
what about you, mister?
Back in my day, I never
let a car stay in the pit
for more than
thirty seconds, tops!
You mean you used to
work on cars, also?!
You're darn right!
In fact, they called me
"Ol' Magic Hands" Sho!
WHAT...?! You're the
legendary magic hands...
You mean a young kid like you
has actually heard about me?!
Yeah! I know all about you!
Hell, the 1975 'Suzuka 8 Hours'
is legendary in our circle!
Damn it all!
Looks like everything
here turned out all right.
Yes.
You've done very well today.
Hey, Belldandy...
I'm sorry you have to
come to all my lectures.
There's no need to apologize,
Keiichi. I really do enjoy it.
As long as I can be with you!
Oh, Belldandy...
Morisato!
What in the world do
you want this time?
--You've gotta help me!
--Ah, there you are, Otaki!
Check this out.
Now here's a good one for ya!
Just take a look at this!
I never would have guessed
that you're a collector, too!
No, really, that's
totally okay, sir!
Don't be shy, son.
After all, I'm going
to be your father soon!
Huh...?!
I'm so terribly sorry, Otaki!
I'm sorry my Dad's so pushy!
You're right, Satoko.
You talk to him about it.
After all, he is going
to be your husband!
Dad, stop it!
C'mon, Otaki. Try this one on.
Wait! Hold on a minute,
President Yamano!
It's not president to you, son!
Call me "Dad!"
Heeeelp meee!
There is someone who wants to
express her feelings for you.
However, those feelings
draw her towards darkness
before she even realizes it.
Next time, "Ah!
Is That Jealousy?"
Is this one of those
so-called "love letters?!"