Dai and I are gonna be attending
the Student Council's budget
meeting this afternoon.
And I want you guys to
straighten this place up
by the time we get back, okay?
Well, Den... Time to go.
Right, Dai! We gotta hustle!
Sure, they tell us to clean
this place up, but the fact is
most of that stuff
belongs to them.
Well, I suppose it
just goes to show you
how much trust they've
placed in you, doesn't it?
Well, to tell you the truth,
I have a feeling
they're just being lazy.
So, do you think we
should get started then?
Sure...
But what do you think should
we do with all this stuff?
I mean, they've stacked
these boxes so precariously
that if we move anything
even a little bit, it could...
Hasegawa!
AAAHHH!
Hasegawa, are you
all right?! Hasegawa!
Ahh!
You didn't hurt
anything, did you?
Kei-Keiichi!
Behind you, just now!
Uh...?
I wonder if that
could've been...?
I'm so relieved to see that
neither of you were injured!
Me, too...
--What the heck was that?
--That was close.
Thanks for your help, Belldandy.
Why, of course, you're welcome.
I might've known.
That is... the one.
Well, I'm gonna go
grab some lunch.
Hm... I guess the reactor's
temperature isn't stable...
But the intensity shouldn't
be that high, though,
so I wonder if...
Success is never accomplished
without experiencing failure.
After all, each failed
attempt only brings you
that much closer to finding the
correct solution, does it not?
But more importantly...
Here! Perhaps if you have some
lunch now it'll cheer you up.
Ah, yeah, you're right.
Hm...? What?
What's this? A letter?
Shiho Sakakibara...
freshman Electronics major?
I've never heard of her.
Let's see...
"I'm sorry to send you a letter
like this out of the blue.
I've been keeping
these feelings inside
since the moment
I first saw you..."
and although I tried many
times to speak to you in person,
I was never actually able
to go through with it.
But today I've
found the courage,
and I want to tell
you how I feel.
Uh...
C-Could this be...
one of those "love letters"
you always hear about?
I mean, I've written one before,
but no one's ever
given one to me!
What's that?
AAAHHH!
I believe letters
are meant to express
the sentiments of
those who write them.
Isn't that correct?
"I will wait in front
of the fountain
until you come to meet me
there. I'll wait forever."
--Urd!
--Keiichi, your such a player!
So... are you gonna
hook up with her?
Huh?! Of course not. I'm not
hooking up with anyone!
Hooking up?
Ah...
Hooking up...
Hm...!
So, what're you gonna do
about this, huh, Keiichi?
I predict she'll be
incredibly cute, too!
Oh. Is that right?
What should I do now...?
What do you think
I should say to her?
Uh, it's not what you think!
I'm not going to "hook up"
with her or anything!
--I'm just going to--
--Keiichi?
Yes?!
I believe that...
it takes a great
amount of energy
in order to express
one's feelings like that.
Therefore, I think you
must respond to her letter!
Ya know, I think I'd kinda like
it if she got a little jealous.
--Keiichi?
--Yeah?!
If we are in agreement,
I think we should go and
respond to her right away.
Uh, yeah...
I guess you're right.
Remember to express
your feelings honestly.
When she said that...
I could see in her eyes
that she really meant it.
But still...
How can she not be jealous
in this kind of situation?
Does she really trust
me so completely?
Or could it possibly be that
I'm not even worth
getting jealous over?
Whoa! She is cute!
What'd I tell ya? I just
knew she was gonna be a cutie.
Man... There's absolutely
no way there's gonna be
an easy way out
of this situation.
What are you talking about?
Look at you blush...
She's your type, isn't she?
How could you say that?!
What do you think, Belldandy?
I think she's a very
beautiful person.
Huh?
And it seems as though
she's looking for someone...
Ah!
I believe she's noticed you.
You did come after all!
Ah!
I'm so glad...!
I was beginning to
think you wouldn't come.
Was... she really the one...?
That sweet, vulnerable
smile of hers
is way too much for me to...
Listen... I was happy to receive
that letter from you, but...
But I...
I'm sorry! But your feelings
for me are just too--
Hold it right there!
Stay where you are!
Huh...?
I knew it!
You have been possessed by
something, after all...!
You're emitting impulses
of energy right now
that are not human!
WHAAAT?!
Don't tell me she knows
about the goddesses!
Ah, yes...! With my power,
I'll send evil spirits
who torment people
back to the darkness!
I'm shivering with excitement
just thinking about it!
Uh...? What... "Evil spirits"?
Just you relax!
Don't worry.
I promise I'll exorcise the evil
spirits that's possessed you!
Uh... so then, you're an
exorcist or something then?
Yes...!
I'm a second year student in
the correspondence program.
Oh, I think I get it now.
So that's what you meant...
"He'll be my first!"
Right! I'm going to
exorcise you now!
Okay! This is getting annoying!
Why are you just
standing there?!
If you're gonna reject her,
then DO it already!
What are you talking about?
Before, you were telling
me to hook up with her!
Oh, come on!
I was just teasing.
I can see it clearly now!
An evil female spirit who
will bring great disaster!
It's not an evil spirit,
it's my living soul!
Belldandy...!
You're also to blame here!
Don't you have anything to say?
You see, Keiichi told me
that he wanted me to
always be here with him...
and that it would be all right
for me to remain by his side.
So I will believe those words,
no matter what else may happen.
I'm sick of this.
Enough is enough...
So this is the place, huh?!
Okay, I'll be going inside to
start my preparations now...
so no peeking, understood?
Come on! I don't understand!
Why are you letting some
crazy stranger use MY room?!
She says it's facing
the right direction.
Direction for doing WHAT?!
For exorcising evil spirits.
AAAH!
You've gotta be kidding me...
Night after night, the
menacing sound of footsteps
echoes down the empty hallway.
Hey, I'm sorry about
this, Belldandy.
This whole ridiculous
situation is because
I wasn't honest with
Shiho from the beginning.
This is not something you
need to apologize for.
But I was... a little
worried about one thing.
I was worried that if Shiho
were really in love with you,
that you would surely have...
ended up... hurting her.
Or am I... wrong to say this?
Mm-mm...
Don't be silly!
Keiichi!
Thank you all for waiting!
That outfit is...
It's nice, isn't it...?
I made it myself, but now...
more importantly...
--Maintain silence.
--Huh?
I am now going to
synchronize our breathing.
Hey! W-Wait... just a minute!
You're... getting too close!
It's poltergeists at work!
Uh...!
You've shown yourselves,
eh, evil spirits?!
So, you wanna mess with me?
Then come and get it!
So, what's all that
stuff for anyway?
Oh... boy...
Just as I thought, I knew
you'd get it wrong...
These actually summon
low-level evil spirits.
Uh...
Why is this kind of stuff
always happening to me?
Belldandy.
Belldandy!
--Yes, what is it, Urd?
--Belldandy?
Come help me peel
off these talismans.
Of course.
Ah...!
It worked...! My talismans
sure did their job, huh?!
A-ha...! So I DO
have the ability!
Thank you! You're the first one!
The first person to go all the
way in helping me with my hobby!
Well... I could tell
from your expression
that you were very
serious about it,
so I couldn't just
turn you down...
And that aspect of
your personality
is part of the
reason I chose you.
Oh...
So then, you really do like
this kind of stuff, huh?
Uh...
Thank you, Keiichi.
Aaahh!
Belldandy!
That was amazing!
It must be a challenge
aimed directly at me,
isn't that right?
Well, I'm a little scared,
but I'll be okay!
Leave it to me!
I'll get rid of all of them this
time, just you wait and see!
Now, the technique that I'm
about to use is a procedure
I just recently learned,
but it's the method
that will give me
the greatest power!
You just sit there and
remain calm, all right?
Um, okay...
Oh, don't worry, you can
leave it up to my genius
to take care of
everything, okay?
You're saying her power escaped?
Yeah. Belldandy lost control.
But why?
You don't know?
Keiichi... how long have you
been with Belldandy now?
She's jealous.
Jealous?
She's not some kind
of doll, you know.
Belldandy experiences those
kinds of emotions, too.
You're kidding.
But she's a goddess, so...
"So she couldn't," is that it?
Falling in love with someone
isn't always pretty...
In fact, it seldom is.
And because she's a goddess...
it hurts her all
the more deeply.
Mm...
You see, this is the first time
that Belldandy has realized...
her own sense of jealousy.
She's so confused
about what to do now.
She could try shutting all
those feelings up inside.
But if she did that, the
outcome would be disastrous
and she'd explode
before too long.
Belldandy...
Why?
I have a whirlwind
of feelings inside,
and I can't manage to
suppress this dark emotion.
What has happened to me?
Somebody... Help me!
Inri... Yod, Nun... Resh, Yod.
Urd!
Oh, come on, Skuld!
Stop being such a pain!
If you're that scared
then get out of here!
But I'd be even more
scared by myself!
Ugh...
Is there anything
the matter... Keiichi?
Ah, it's no big deal really...
But I was just thinking that...
Yes?
I want you to know
that I never...
intended for things to
turn out the way they have.
It's all my fault for not being
more upfront with her
in the first place.
And I really hope
you understand that
it's nothing you
should take to heart.
Keiichi...
Keiichi!
I now require total silence.
It won't be much longer.
Oh... I'm sorry...
No! I'm so scared!
Inri. Yod, Nun, Resh.
Yod, Nun, Resh.
--No! No! NO! Please stop!
--Isis... Apophi... Osiris...
I... A... O!
ARARITA!
Hey, Urd, are you sure
she knows what she's doing?
What would I know about
a worthless incantation
like that one?
GRRR!
Wait, isn't that...
I really did it! I have
awakened the Kundalini!
Whaaat?!
I am called Garm.
I am the watchdog over
the dark world Niflheim.
No!
You will state your intent...
Looks like she's really
done it this time.
Actually, you're not
the one I was calling.
You idiot!
Such flagrant audacity!
You have dared to summon the
mighty Garm without reason?!
I'm only saying you're
not who I was summoning.
Ten thousand deaths would
not be enough for you!
Ah! Urd!
Grr... rawr!
Skuld, hurry!
Get those symbols erased!
I'm scared...
They're written
in permanent marker,
so they're not coming off!
Then rewrite them as
an anti-demonic program!
I don't know how to write
those kinds of formulas!
Rawr!
No! At this rate,
we're gonna be...
An anti-demonic program
won't work on Garm.
We must use a
banishment program.
Belldandy!
I have to keep fighting him off!
Belldandy...
you'll have to do it!
Belldandy!
Hey, are you okay?
It's no use. I don't
know it... I can't move...
I'm so scared...! It won't
erase...! Please stop this!
Grrrr!
It's no use...
He's way too strong!
Hold on!
Be careful!
I've reached my limit!
Grr...! Rawr!
Oh, no, Urd!
Keiichi, save me!
You're strangling me!
Rawr!
Grr... What was that?!
--Belldandy!
--I'm really scared!
Was that me...? Did I just...?
I see...
All that pent up jealousy must
have weakened Belldandy's seal.
If she could hit Garm
directly with that power...
she would be able
to send him back.
But then...
I'm sorry, Belldandy, I'm going
to have to play a little dirty.
Forgive me.
Grr...
Aaaahhh! No! Keiichi!
Please do something! Aaaaahh!
Rawr...!
AAAAHHH!
Summon!
Remote Human
Manipulation technique!
Keiichi, I'm... really sorry.
Ah! Why the hell am
I doing this to her?!
I understand.
I was... so afraid...
Rawr...!
Belldandy!
Grr!
Belldandy...
I'm truly a terrible person...
I thought I was concerned about
her feelings being hurt...
but the real truth
of the matter is that
I was actually more
afraid of losing you.
Despite the fact I told you that
I have complete faith in you.
Belldandy...
Keiichi...! You must
really hate me now!
No, that's not true!
I'm the one who
should be apologizing!
Because... I was wrong to take
your trust in me for granted.
Urd explained to me that
falling in love with someone
isn't always pretty,
and I understand that now.
Maybe being in love
with someone means...
that you want to be with
that person all the time...
no matter if you're upset
or crying or laughing.
Look, Belldandy...
I hope you understand that your
the only one I want to be with.
Oh, Keiichi...
Oh, thank you!
Belldandy...
Oh, Keiichi...
I know I planned
all this myself,
so what in the world is
this strange itchy feeling?
--I did it!
--Uh?
This serves as absolute proof
that I really am
a genius after all!
I will continue to
use this awesome power
to make everyone happy!
Thank you so much for helping!
The fact she was
able to summon Garm...
might make her a genius,
even if she did it by mistake...
What did you say?!
You should be
grateful just to...
Obsessive, overconfident,
inexperienced, and cocky...
Yep. Those two are birds
of a feather all right.
I'll tell you something
about geniuses...
You happen to be looking at one!
Oh? And what exactly
makes YOU a genius, hm?
Care to give me a demonstration?
Okay, you asked for it!
Here I go!
It should have been
just another mistake.
Appearing with
the scent of roses,
she rejects their
unexpected reunion.
Next time, "Ah!
I Shall Grant Your Wish."
Yes, we know that your
service is the best in Heaven.