Hey! Just what the
heck is going on?!
You've... gotta be kidding me!
Hild?
Hm? Oh, Bell, I just started
some of my home-cooking.
Would you like
to try some, too?
What are you talking about?!
And just what do you
think you're doing
waltzing into our house and
using our kitchen anyway?!
Hey, Hild?
Is breakfast ready yet? I'm so
hungry I could eat a horse!
What are you talking about?
It'll be just a little
longer, darling!
Now be a good boy
and wait patiently.
Well, I can't wait to try
whatever it is you've
made this time.
Just be sure to let me
know when it's ready, okay?
Sure thing!
Hey! Get back here,
Keiichi! Keiichi!
Why is Keiichi acting like this?
Here. Now say "ah."
Aaah...
Now I think I understand
what's going on.
I was totally wrong
about you, Keiichi!
How could you two-time Big
Sis with that rotten, Hild?!
AH, I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE!
Just what is the matter
with you, Keiichi?!
With me...? What do you mean?
Don't try being coy with me!
How could you do this
when you've got Big Sis?!
Although technically I suppose
Big Sis is still mine...
But still!
What are you
talking about, Skuld?
Here, why don't you try some
of this? It's really good!
Like I'd ever try
any of Hild's food!
Of course, I mean
what would you do
if it actually turned out to
be better than Belldandy's?
There's no way
that could happen!
Would you care to take
a little taste test?
Then perhaps you
can see for yourself
whether it's better or not.
Uh-oh.
AAHHH!
Oh, my. Maybe the
flavor profiles were
a tad too intense for a child.
There's no sign he's under
any kind of control, is there?
Correct.
Oh, you've got a speck
of food on your face.
Hey, cut it out.
We shouldn't act like this in
front of Urd and Belldandy.
And why not?
I'm sure they're both very happy
for us, Keiichi. Aren't you?
All right, that's enough...!
I don't know what
your scheme is here,
but if you make
Belldandy angry--
Oh, no.
That is the rising dragon!
Oh, my... Nanmaida, nanmaida...
Uh, are you okay, Belldandy?
Still just a girl deep down,
aren't you, Bell?
Keiichi...
That's quite a lump of
earwax I just extracted!
Well, I guess I haven't cleaned
out my ears in a while.
I'm not picking anything up.
There aren't any signs of
a spell being used on him.
But is there any
chance that Keiichi
may have been
possessed by a demon?
No, it's not that either.
That's the real Keiichi.
Do you think he could
have been given something,
like a seed of love,
or some kind of potion?
I look into that too
but there's no indication
that he's been given
any kind of drug.
Then, Keiichi and Hild,
truly are in love?
No, there's definitely
something going on here.
I'm sure of it.
Hey, Keiichi.
You know, it's been a while
since we've had a bath together.
Ah... But I...
You do wanna take
one with me right?
Oh no, it's not that I don't
want to or anything.
It's just that I'm a little
embarrassed. That's all.
But why? We're
in love aren't we?
So I really don't see
what the big deal is.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Ahh?!
This is bad!
If Belldandy see them
together in the bath,
everything in the area
will be totally obliterated.
What are we gonnaa do?!
Ugh! We'll beat her there and
prevent it from happening!
Ahh!
Would you rather see this
whole place blown to bits?
I... will do what I can...
Ugh! To think of what I have
to deal with around here.
Hello, Urd.
Oh, hey! What's up?
Sorry, but we're kind of in the
middle of something right now.
Look at this.
Huh?
Now, Keiichi, why don't we start
with washig each other's backs?
Ahhh!!!
You're such a pervert, Keiichi!
Stop looking and just
get outta here already.
Ok! Sorry about that
Just hold on.
You've got nothing
to be sorry about.
Well, she's only
a child after all.
What did you just call me?!
Now, listen Skuld, sweetie,
you shouldn't worry about that
until later down the road
once you're all grown up.
Holy...
Now then, Keiichi...
Uh-huh.
Come on over here.
Uh...
No!!
Oh my! You shouldn't
fall asleep there.
You'll catch a cold.
What exactly did
you do to Keiichi?
Why I haven't done
anything to him.
We're simply in
love. That's all.
There's no way that's true.
So what did I do to him then?
Hmm?
Well, I don't exactly...
Ok! That's quite enough.
Oh, why hello, Urdie.
Oh, Keiichi!
Please tell me you're all right!
I think it's high time
you did a little explaning.
Whatever do you mean?
Belldandy found this
interesting little item.
Wow! That was faster
than I expected.
Why would you possibly
want to do this?
Iis it Keiichi's
heart youre after
or something else?
Good question.
I guess I just
did it on a whim.
Just a whim?
Because you felt like it,
Well, if you don't like it
then why not see if
you can get him back?
He is your Keiichi, right?
Are you ok?
Is that you Hild?
Where am I?
Belldandy...
Let's all go together
and get your Keiichi back.
But Urd...
Y'know, she doesn't seem
the least bit concerned
about what we're doing.
Will this really work?
What's really getting to
me is seeing how much
she's enjoying all this.
Keiichi...
Ooo, I just love that
look in her eyes.
It's giving me the chills.
Are you ready Urd?
Let's do this.
I am the goddess Urd.
In the name of the goddesses who
govern the passage of time,
guide us into the past,
into the point we seek.
It's so cold.
Where the heck are we anyway?
We're in the town where
Keiichi was born and grew up.
The town where he was born?
So this is where
Keiichi used to live?
Keiichi...
Oh man, I guessed I
shouldn't have fooled around
with the engine.
I'll never be able
to beat him like this.
Just look at him!
Young Keiichi is so cute!
Yohoo! Keiichi!
Ugh! What do you
think you're doing?
Don't be such a fool.
Keiichi has met us
yet in this time
so he's obivoulsy not gonna
know who we are.
Oh! You're right. I forgot.
Good Morning, Keiichi.
Oh, uh, good morning.
Engine break down again?
Yeah, I'm ashamed to admit it.
Hey! Kei, see you
when you get home, eventually!
Haha! Later! Wohoo!
That Keima sure has
a really nice bike.
But even so,
you'll beat him some day.
That's right;
you better believe it.
Oh, Keiichi. I'm freezing.
Can you believe
those two flirting
with each other like that?
What is he thinking?
Well you can hardly blame him.
From what I can tell it doesn't
seem like he was very popular
with the girls
back then, does it?
And yet, she's already managed
to get acquainted with him.
She's reading our moves
and adjusting accordingly.
If we go back in time again,
she'll just got even farther
back and meet Keiichi then.
I'm afraid it's quite simple for
the ruler of demon kind.
But... What should we do?
We have to take a stand here
and try to turn Keiichi's
attention towards you.
If it's the only way...
All right. Quiet down, everyone.
This is a bit sudden but
I've got a new student
to introduce to you.
Her name is Belldandy.
She just transfered here,
so please try to make
her feel at home.
Hello. My name's Belldandy.
It's very nice to
meet all of you.
All right, Ryuta. Settle down.
Anyway, as I was saying, please
give Belldandy a hand if you see
that she needs help with
anything for the next few days.
But why do I have to pretend
to be in Elementary school?
Because, you
simply look the part.
That's why.
Well, I'll have you
know that I'm an adult,
so I should be on the...
You've already been registered
as an Elementary School
transfer student,
so there's nothing I can do.
No run along to
class, young lady.
I hate you, Urd!!!
Now, have a look at
the triangle on the left.
If we draw a line from
point A to points B and C...
This is the kind of
situation that calls
for writing him a letter.
Then find a descreet
way of slipping it to him.
Right. Well that's
all for today then.
This material will be on the
test, so be sure to review it.
Excuse me.
Hmm?
Ah! Sorry about earlier.
I wasn't really
staring at you see...
Uh... Uhm... It's just that I
thought you were kinda pretty
and so I was...
Keiichi.
Woulld you mind showing
me your math notes?
Oh! Uh, sure no problem.
Uh... Let's see...
Oh, there it is,
My, you have such
nice handwriting.
Really? Huh... I never
thought it was that good.
Excuse me.
Can we help you with something?
Well, I just...
Oh look at you Keiichi.
You've got bed head again.
Come on. Let's get going.
Sure...
See you later.
Ah, excuse me.
What's going on?
Never mind. It's noithing.
Uhmm...
Come on. Let's forget about
reading and go play basketball.
Please excuse me.
It's just that I was
hoping to give you..
Keiichi!
What's taking you
so long in there?
We gotta go!
Coming!
If I can just...
Keiichi!
Keiichi...
Why? Why can't I capture just
the tiniest bit of courage?
You still haven't
given it to him?
You can't allow her
to get in the way
and obstruct what
you're trying to do.
I know that but I just
couldn't find the courage.
Well the first thing you have to
do is get yourself more noticed.
Shoot hima few amorous
looks now an then.
Or you could even
fall over on purpose
so he can see up your skirt.
Or ask him what kind of
girls he is interested in.
I dunno. All of
this feels so wrong.
It feels like there is a black
cloud over my heart
and it's filled with so
many negative emotions.
Jealousy, huh?
No, of course not!
Well, regardless,
whatever it is,
it's clearly not
working for you.
All right then.
This calls for a
change of plans.
Leave her to me.
You just concetrate
on telling Keiichi
how you really feel about him.
You can manage that much right?
Or rather, you haave to manage
that much, or we're in trouble.
Right.
Hey, Skuld. We're heading
over to the kid's store.
Wanna come with us?
What's the kid's store?
A candy shop.
They've got tons of
toys and candy there
and I'll be happy to buy
you some if you want.
Will you really?
Sure I'll go!!
Maybe Elementary School
isn't so bad after all.
Hmm?
What's going on down there?
How about we go do something
on the way home today?
Well, I'm afraid I don't have
any money on me today...
Actually, I'd like to have a
little word with you.
So that's how it's
gonna be, huh?
I uhm... I don't know what
Hild might have done to
upset you so much but I'll
be happy to hear you out.
So would you mind
just putting that down?
Keiichi...
It's all right. You don't
need to get involved in this.
Why don't you run on home?
I'll catch up with you later.
But I don't think...
I said go.
Hild?
All right. If that's
how you wanna play it.
And I was just starting
to get bored here.
I'll be impressed Urdie,
if you can last five minutes.
That's not too shabby.
If you keep
underestimating me like that,
it might prove costly.
Ahh! What's going on the
breaks aren't responding?!
Oh no! Waaaahh!!
Are you all right, Keiichi?
Keiichi?
Oh, sorry.
I didn't think you knew my
first name since we just met.
I'm sorry, Mr. Morisato.
Oh, it's ok. You can call
me Keiichi, if you want.
Well, uhmm, actually...
Huh?
I, uhm...
Uhm...
You see...
I... I'd like to...
You see the truth is th--
Keiichi!
Oh, uh, hey, Hild!
Just what do you think you're
doing standing out here
talking to some other girl
behind my back, hmm?
Well, I fell off my bike.
Oh no! Are you all right?
I'm sorry, Belldandy.
She was just
too powerful for me.
Come on. We can't act
like this in front of her.
Why not just say it?
Tell us your true feelings.
Tell you my true feelings?
That's right.
You utterly hate me, don't you?
For taking the one you love the
most and making him my own.
And for turning him into
my own little plaything...
Hey! Hold on!
A little boy like this...
Huh?
What are you doing?
You just hold still now...
No!!!
Now that's what
I'm talking about.
Those are your true feelings
and your true power.
Now, why don't you go ahead
and release those feelings?
Release all my feelings?
Anger, hatred, jealousy...
Stop suppressing it.
I want you to hit me
with all those feelings.
But I...
If you just release it, Keiichi
will come back to you.
And you can have
him all to yoursef.
Now, show me what you've got!
But I mustn't... I'm a goddess.
Release all the
emotion and power.
Let go and release everything!
But I mustn't!
I was wondering.
Do you like the snow?
I sure do.
It's pure and white
and I dunno; it just has a way
of making me feel peaceful.
And I think, that for some
reason or another,
it seems to suit
you really well too.
Huh?
It's called diamond dust.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
It is.
It can't be.
I don't believe it.
Hild?
I think we need to have a talk.
See ya later!
Hmm?
Huh? Big Sis?
Big Sis!
Oh Skuld!
What are you doing
standing out here all alone?
I may... I may...
have done something
I probably shouldn't have.
What happened, Big Sis?
Skuld...
Oh, Big Sis...
But why?
Because... you don't
really like me, right?
Maybe we could just be friends.
To think that a mere human
could have realized that.
That's Keiichi for you.
Hmm?
Hello, Urdie.
He'd do anything for Belldandy.
Place a call to the Almighty
in Heaven...
Protect her from the
peskiest of demons...
And go anywhere for her without
fear for his own wellbeing...
That's just the
kind of guy he is.
Well, that's too bad.
I have to say I was
really looking forward
to seeing Belldandy's
true feelings.
What? They aren't
obvious to you?
Her true feelings are
actually quite easy to see.
Huh?
Well, let's just say these
true inner feelings are...
Would you...
Belldandy, I... Uhm...
Uh-huh?
Would you... Would you like to
go visit the museum with me?
Does that mean
that you wouldn't?
Sure, I'll go.
Five years from now.
Huh? What?
Hang on...
What the heck am
I doing out here anyway?
Five years? What the heck's
that supposed to mean?
What gives?
Where'd Big Sis go?
She and Keiichi decided
to go out for a while.
Just leave them alone, Skuld.
At least for today, ok?
It's amazing!
I wonder what color
this dinosaur was.
If I remember correctly,
I believe these were
originally brownish grey.
Haha! Is that right?
Huh?
Hey, Belldandy?
Do you like that snow?
Yes.
Then we should really
go visit my hometown.
Maybe sometime next winter.
Are you feeling ok?
You bet.
A long forgotten promise...
But she remembers,
hoping that it might
stil come true some day.
Next time, "Ah!
Everyone has a Destiny"
You've waited for me all
this time... haven't you?