What is this?
What's going on?
What just happened?
It's not a dream or an illusion.
I trust Keiichi, but...
but I... I don't know what
Urd's feelings really are!
What about... what
about my feelings?
Your innocence is
your fatal flaw.
You're the same as he is.
At the very least I can
take some pity on you,
my little sister, by
having you sleep on and on
in tranquility... for eternity!
Look out, Big Sis!
Don't let her fool you!
She's an imposter!
But how can there be two Urds?
Skuld, what do you mean
she's an imposter?
Uh, well strictly speaking
they're both technically
the real Urd, only...
Now look here, Urd.
I don't know what you
think you were doing
pulling a stunt like that,
but if Belldandy gets upset...
Uh... am I seeing things?
Are there really two Urd's?
What did she divide,
like a cell or something?
Hold on, lemme think here.
Maybe she has a long
lost twin sister,
and they've just
finally been reunited.
No, no, it's not like that!
That is my Demonic half
which Mara managed
to separate from me!
Huh?
This is getting to be a pain.
Mara put a pretty
half-assed seal
on my other half, didn't she?
She's right you know.
I had Urd restrained with
a program that only works
on Half Goddess
Half Demon hybrids.
So if her Divine
side were isolated,
the seal would lose its effect.
A fault, an abnormality,
a blunder,
unbelievable and
unforeseen, oh yeah!
Depth-charge, or some
very nasty medicine.
Which is to be your
pleasure, dearies?
Now that Urd is in her
fully Demonic form,
I wouldn't be surprised
if she uses her power
without any restraint.
So I'll leave the
rest to you, Senbei.
Nein, nyet, no way Jose,
that's not fair,
if we're going down,
we'll go down together!
Ah, they'll find us,
you numbskull!
I know you are, but what am I?
This is a safe
assumption, come...
I guess they'll be
getting the depth charge
and the nasty medicine later.
It can't be.
If Mara was able to
separate the Divine
and Demonic halves of Urd,
which is something even
the Almighty One Himself
couldn't do, then the
Demonic half of Urd
would possess the most
awful, evil powers.
If her power continues unchecked
and goes out of control,
the sheer magnitude
of that energy
will collapse upon itself,
and devastate everything
in the surrounding area.
You must go back to how
you were right away Urd!
If you don't, then I'm
afraid your body will...
My voice!
Hey, what's the
matter? Belldandy?
Did something happen
to Urd's body?
That information
has been protected!
The separation of Demon
and Divine falls under
"topics of special
significance"!
This leaves me no choice.
Ha ha, how do you like that?!
Oh great.
Now we don't know which
one's the Good Urd!
Please don't be fooled
guys, I'm the Good Urd!
Don't listen to her,
I'm really the Good Urd!
That's not enough
for us to go by.
Now this is the kind of
thing where you find out
by looking into their eyes.
I just saw something
really creepy!
If you are the real one,
then you should know
where Keiichi hides his
dirty magazines, right?
Yes. You see, after Peorth
found them, he moved them
to the third drawer of
the desk in his room.
Well then what about
the chocolates he got
from Belldandy last year?
He thought they were
too good to be eaten,
so he stashed them away in
the treasure box in his closet.
When did you look into that?!
What does Keiichi do
before going to bed?
He kisses a picture
of Belldandy goodnight.
Be quiet!
Okay, what does he do
in front of the mirror
when he gets up each morning?
He touches the cheek that
Belldandy kissed and grins.
Next question?
Hey, wait a minute! Why is it
all private stuff about me?
And both of you are
the real one, anyway.
Hm. I've got it now!
Wha?! Hey, what was that?!
You're the Demonic Urd,
I knew it all along!
That's not nice at all!
You know perfectly well
I'm the Good Urd!
Sorry, but you can't
fool us anymore.
Because you see, the Good Urd
has a mark right here
that I put on her!
Hah. Not too shabby.
Well, for a kid at least.
Huh?! For a kid?!
You called me a kid again!
No Skuld, stop!
Even if she is a Demon,
Urd is still your sister.
Whatever happens
we cannot allow Urd
to lose that half of herself.
Because if she does...
Both Urds will be destroyed.
Yes, that's right,
I am indeed your sister.
And that is exactly why you
won't be getting rid of me.
However...
I have no problem
getting rid of you!
--Help me sister!
--Please, Belldandy!
Oh Spirits, heed my
wish and my command.
Protect these innocents
and shield them from harm!
But you know I really
have to wonder.
Can you hold up as well
through another round?
Will you release your seal then?
You can't do that
while you're chanting
your defensive spell, can you?
Stop it Urd! Please, stop!
Now, be a good sister and
become one with the heavens!
Depth charge!
Explosive electro shock blast!
It can't be! That was
an upper level two spell.
Even more advanced than
the depth charge descent.
Yes, it was.
It's true that those three
can't get rid of you.
However, I cannot allow you
to get rid of them either.
Even if that means becoming
only half of my former self.
Even if it means that
I must lose everything.
Hah, fine with me.
Give it your best shot!
But you're the one
who's going down, not me!
Yeah, well we'll see about that!
Ahhh!
Stop it Urd! Don't do it!
Huh? Huh!
Oh man!
What's the matter?
You look like you're moving
pretty slow over there.
This is bad.
At this rate they'll all
get caught up in this!
Aahhh!
You must stop this!
Skuld!
Keiichi!
As long as you've got
someone to protect,
you'll never defeat me!
Okay, let's do it.
Bring it on!
This is...
Not good!
Here comes a big one!
Bye bye.
What the?!
Huh?
What's... happening?
Could it already be... starting?
Why does... my body feel so...
Oh crap!
I knew you were behind
this all along, Mara!
Anti-Mara missile....
FIRE!
She got away.
Poor Urd.
She couldn't withstand
her own power.
It's because that body
of hers, unfortunately,
was produced... artificially.
What is this?!
What is this pain?!
Uh, milady Mara,
isn't the situation
getting a little... bad?
At this rate, Urd's not
gonna last much longer!
Come on Senbei, it's time to go!
Go? But where are
we going, milady?
Just come with me!
You two!
Yes?
Do something about this pain!
Ugh. My body.
I must get my real body!
Well I guess that outta do it.
Banpei should be all right now!
I can't believe Urd has
such amazing abilities
when there's no
restrictions on her power.
Unfortunately there's
a lot more to it than that.
It appears that since that
body of hers is artificial
it just can't meet the demands
of casting such
a powerful spell.
Are you saying she's
some kind of a clone?
That is why
I am certain that the Demonic
Urd will eventually return.
To try and take back my body.
Oh, Urd, but...
At this rate the Demonic Urd
will go out of control.
Belldandy?
What's wrong, Big Sis?
It's no use. I simply
can't say the words!
You mustn't strain yourself.
But... Urd.
This falls under "special
significance", doesn't it?
Uh, "special significance"?
Listen Belldandy;
all you have to do
is shake your head 'yes', okay?
My Demonic half
will eventually go
completely out of
control, won't it?
And then it will
unleash the kind of power
that could destroy the Earth.
That's it, isn't it?
Plus, the loss of control over
her own power will destroy her.
Even if it is her
real body she uses.
Urd, wait!
I already had a vague suspicion.
You see throughout
my whole life,
the Good and Evil
halves within me
have always been
in constant conflict.
I have one last question: do
you suppose that it's possible
for light to exist
without darkness?
I thank you, Belldandy.
Hey! What's that
supposed to mean?
Mara!
I think she's hurt!
We have to help her quick!
Just forget about that.
This is more important.
Take this.
I can't believe I'm
about to say this but...
I want you to use
this to save her.
Urd's lost it.
If she keeps on using
her power like that,
the replica body won't last.
You've got to do something!
Has she already begun
to go out of control?
The truth is... that I
can't afford to lose her.
Because... I haven't
beaten her at Breakout yet.
Sayonara, everybody.
If she really does
self-destruct,
who knows what repercussions
it will have on this Urd.
So please, I'm begging you.
Just save her!
When she said 'Light
without Darkness',
does that mean that she...
Please Urd, you mustn't
destroy the Demonic Urd!
I don't believe it!
Whether she's Good or Evil,
she's still just as stubborn!
I'm sorry, but my power simply
wasn't enough to stop her.
Hold on.
This is no time to be getting
depressed and down on yourself.
If you wanna help Urd, then
tell us the separation program
you used to divide them.
We can use that to come up
with a unification routine.
Oh, right!
And you, the little
guy over there!
Go inside and gather all
the parts that look like
they might work in a
'Urd-Fusion Machine.'
Gotcha! Yes ma'am!
Your wish is my command!
We're going to save Urd,
no matter what it takes!
Besides, I still
need to get her back
for always getting to
choose what we watch on TV!
My body...
If I just had my real body!
And where do you
think you're going?
If I'm not mistaken,
it's this real body that
you're after, isn't it?
Wow, she's already forgotten
her original objective.
I guess that's
just the way I am.
It's no use, I need to get
her to use more of her power.
I'm not really sure what you're
aiming at, but I'm over here!
Before she goes
completely out of control,
I need to push her to the
point of self-destruction,
beyond the limits
of that cloned body!
There they are!
Hurry up, or
she'll be done for!
All right, hang on!
Jeez, that Urd is such an idiot.
Why does she always have to go
so overboard with everything?
Damn! Come back!
Still no good.
Yes, that's it, just keep
using more of your power!
How about... this?!
Just a little more!
So. I guess that's it for me.
Still. That had to have
depleted a lot of her energy.
The rest is up to them.
That's...
I've got you Urd!
Forget about me.
I'm fine. Just hurry!
Don't worry about her.
From now on, I just
need you to do as we say.
If we can get her to use
just a little more power...
we might be able to get my
Demonic half to destroy herself.
But we can't do that!
Skuld...
We can't do it, because we're
going to save the both of you
no matter what!
Just this once...
I just wish you'd listen
to me, just this once!
All right, I will.
I guess I can't call
you a kid anymore.
So have you got that?
Lure the Demonic Urd
to this marker.
We'll figure out
what to do from there.
Where could she be hiding?
You can't hide forever!
Come out here with my real body!
There she is, down there.
What is that?
Hmm.
Come down here and get me,
you cloned pile of junk!
The real me is right
here waiting for you!
What, done running?
Are you ready to give
that body over to me?
How about you?
How are you feeling?
You must be hurting
all over, huh?
That'll be taken
care of real soon.
As soon as I get my
body back that is!
You just don't know
when to give up, do you?
I think perhaps it might be time
for you to get yourself ready.
Ready for what?
Ready to go back to Heaven.
All right then. I see how it is.
In that case, we'll see
who's destined to die!
Activate!
Hah, oh please!
I was wondering what
kind of silly contraption
you'd rigged up.
And there's another one!
No way!
That's just the kind of thing
I'd expect from Skuld.
Talk about truly pathetic.
So are you out of ideas now?
Looks like you're the one
who's going down after all!
So hand over that
body right now!
Wha?
What is this?!
All right!
So, how'd you like
the Urd-Eater I made?
It kinda looks like something
out of a B-grade Horror movie.
All right now Urd.
We're gonna reunify you two,
so get in on the opposite side.
--I can't do it.
--Huh?
My Demonic half
tried to kill you.
If I were to go back
to the way I was before,
I'll have that Evil
inside of me.
I just can't go back
to being that person.
I'm so sorry... for everything.
It's all right.
The truth of all of this is
that the Demonic Urd never
did truly want to kill us.
The Demonic Urd with
her unrestricted power
should have been able to cast as
powerful a spell as she wanted.
And yet, all she cast was a
depth charge descent spell.
That's because she intentionally
suppressed her own power.
Even when you were
completely overrun by Evil,
you were still the same old Urd.
So you can go back to being
the big sister we all love.
So are you two all
set in there, Urd?
Okay then. Commencing
reunification.
So, are you sure
this is really gonna
put her back to the way she was?
It'll be all right. We must
have faith in our little Skuld.
Please go back to
being your old self.
Hey guys, I'm back
to norm-- Whoa, hey!
Oh, Urd! Welcome back!
Oh Urd, it's good to see you!
Well, it's good to
be back. Thanks guys!
Oh, how beautiful!
Such gorgeous, adoring sisters.
Come on. I think it's
time we left, Senbei.
Stop right there!
You had a lot of nerve to
run off and abandon me earlier.
So, you value that heretical
pact more than me, do you?
What?
Come on, we're gonna
drink up a storm!
Mara, you're getting off
your butt and coming with us.
But if we're going
to drink, what I'd like
is some of that yummy
tea Belldandy made.
What are you talking about?
When you're pooped,
there's nothing like
the highest quality,
unprocessed Saki!
What happened to her?
It's kinda like there are
two Urd's in one body now!
Hey Skuld I don't get it,
why are the Demonic
and the Divine
personalities still separate?
Mara!
Didn't you put the routine
together properly?
Now that you mention it,
maybe there actually was
a problem with some of the
parts that Senbei brought you.
Perish the thought; I carried
out my task to utter perfection!
Come on! Let's go
back, Belldandy.
Back to our home!
Sure, let's go!
Jeez, how did this happen?!
Urd's not gonna be a
Demon anymore, is she?
I'm going to be a Goddess,
through and through.
That may have been
my aspiration.
Next time... 'Ah! The Chair
of Demonkind Descends!'
That's Urd's mother?!
Nice to meet you!