So what do we do now?
This is so bad...
I mean, this is really bad...
It can't be.
That's someone I didn't think...
...would ever come back here.
Hm...
Hey Keiichi, do you know what's
the matter with those two?
No...
MORISATO!
Yes, what is it?
The two of us are gonna
lay low for a while.
And don't you dare tell
anyone where we are either.
But who are we gonna tell?
We don't even know
where you're going...
Just don't tell anyone!
So, adieu, lady
and gentlemen.
Um... Why are you taking
so much stuff with you?
Oh...
What's the heck's goin' on?
It's been a long time...
Those adjustments should help to
increase the engine's power.
I wonder if it'll run okay...
All that's left is to
take it for a test run
and see if there's
any improvement.
I can hardly wait to see!
You've certainly come
a long way with it.
Uh-huh... We're almost ready
to do a shakedown test.
Well, before you go do that...
why don't we all take
a short break, okay?
That's so nice of you!
And there are delicious
sweets to go with the tea.
--Awesome!
--All right!
Things haven't changed.
WHA...?!
What the hell's going on?!
I'm not kidding. It's true!
2400 CCs?!
No, I'm serious!
It really was that big--
HEY!
Tamiya! Otaki!
What the hell's the
meaning of this?!
Um, excuse me, but who are you?
Stop staring at me and tell me
where Tamiya and
Otaki have gone.
The seniors ran outta
here a little while ago.
Damn.
They probably figured I'd come
without any advance notice...
Well, never mind...
You, there. Come with me.
Who gave you
permission to do that?
Did you know this vehicle
is the Auto Club's baby?
A treasure passed down from year
to year since the club began!
And therefore I--
Ah... ah...
Oh, my... it's beautiful!
Huh?
It's amazing...! Is it
a radio-controlled bike?
Well, no. I'm gonna ride it.
You're gonna ride it?
How come?
Well, we, uh wanted to
investigate the possibilities
of an ultra-small-scale
internal combustion engine...
Huh?
That's the "official"
story, at least.
The truth is we
thought it would be cool
if someone could ride a
radio-controlled vehicle.
Talk about easy...! That's
so simple it's ridiculous!
Ah, I can't breathe!
W-What? Are you saying 'cause
it's simple, it's no good?
What's so bad about
it being simple?
Look, it seemed like
it'd be fun, okay?
And that's why we're doing it.
Don't you think that's
more than enough reason
to start this kind of project?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make fun of
what you guys are trying to do.
Years ago...
there was a guy
standing right here,
who said the same kind of
thing that you're saying now.
Said the same thing?
You there. You've got a
good eye... What's your name?
Keiichi Morisato, Junior in
Mechanical Engineering.
I see... You're Morisato,
huh...? I like you, kid.
Hey, how about I make
another one of these,
and we have ourselves
a little race?
You wanna have a race?
You don't want to?
Well, this is all
kinda sudden, y'know?
Let's just say, meeting you
has put me in the mood to race.
Not enough of a reason?
I guess it's fine, but...
I think it's a wonderful idea.
Huh?
I'm certain it would be
much more fun to have
two people riding them
rather than just one person.
If you think something is fun,
then I believe
that mere enjoyment
is reason enough to do it.
I like your thinking!
What's your name?
Oh, my name is Belldandy.
Okay, so Morisato and "Bell"...
I'm really glad we
got a chance to meet.
So, we'll have the race
right here in one week, okay?
But, um...
What's the matter?
Does that not work for you?
No, it's just that we still
don't know who you are.
Oh, right... I never
did introduce myself.
I'm Ex-Club Manager Chihiro
Fujimi... Nice to meet you.
See ya later!
It turns out that
Ms. Fujimi is the one
who took a small group of
like-minded enthusiasts
and elevated them to "Auto Club"
status at Nekomi Tech.
The very first club manager...
Whoa, this is amazing!
Unbelievable!
All-Japan Dirt Trial Runner-Up
and First in the All-Japan
Gymkhana Championship?!
You're kidding...
Third in the Student
Formula SAE Competition
and First in the Six-hour
endurance race?!
Oh, maybe that's where Tamiya
and Otaki came into the picture.
I bet that kind of rigorous
racing environment
made them who they are today.
WHAT?! She came in Third place
in the amateur class
in the Suzuka 8 Hours?!
Yeah! She participated
as an amateur
in the Paris-Dakar Rally, too!
Hey, Keiichi, she raced
in the Sahara, too!
There are pictures of it!
So basically she was a
totally incredible person,
is that right?
It sure looks that way!
Plus, she worked in
the motorsports division
of a motorcycle manufacturer
after she graduated.
So, do you think we
even stand a chance
against someone so amazing?
I honestly don't know.
Ms. Fujimi just came
in here and said that
she wanted to have
a race against us...
but it's not like I really know
anything about her though,
so it's hard to say...
Don't you want to race?
Huh?
It's nothing to
do with that...
It's just, that's not
why I built this bike.
Encounters like this...
are never merely
coincidence, Keiichi.
I'm sure there must be
some important reason
for the two of you
meeting each other today.
I wonder...
--Aaaaah!
--Huh?
Hey, come check out
this old photo!
Tamiya and Otaki
look so young here!
I'll bet this picture is
from when their group was
raised to official club
status at the university.
Look at that smile.
She must have been really happy.
Oh, now that really
takes me back.
Aahh! You were standing
right there the whole time?!
Sorry to bother you, but could
I borrow that box end wrench?
Uh, yeah, sure...
Thanks!
What are you going
to use it for?
Well, I couldn't just leave
my baby out there like that...
Oh...
Whoa...
She's fixing it?!
Man! This part's broken, too!
How the heck did she
lower the engine?!
--There's no brake fluid!
--I don't believe it!
Who the hell tuned
this suspension?!
Those guys still
don't know jack.
Belldandy?
Yes?
I think I understand it now...
what it is that you
were trying to tell me.
I'm glad!
I kinda think we'd be in
different classes...
Don't worry about that!
Besides, you're the one
who wanted some practice,
so stop complaining!
Don't be intimidated
by its looks.
I mean, it's only a
child's toy after all.
I am not a child and
Banpei isn't a toy!
Yeah, yeah...
We're gonna show ya...!
This is the Banpei
Hybrid Hydrogen-Powered
Extra-Special Model... GO!
Wait a second!
Good. The bike feels right...
Aaaahh!
This tuning is going to
have a negative impact
on the engine's longevity.
I guess winning is gonna take
more than just horsepower...
What the heck are you doing?!
This is why I said it's
just a child's toy, Skuld.
But Banpei...
You can't lose to
something like that!
Waaahh!
Wow...
Well, I guess I
must've forgotten
to erase his attack program.
Now, listen, you...
Keiichi!
Hey...
I came to see if you're okay...
I heard a terrible
crash just now!
Uh-huh, yeah,
I'm okay, thanks...
And the bike's even
all right, too. See?
Oh, good, what a relief!
But if you don't mind, Keiichi,
I have a favor I'd
like to ask of you.
Oh. What is it?
An engine swap?!
What? Are you kidding me?!
We'll never have
it set up in time,
even if we start right now!
Our team's sponsor has
put in a very firm request.
The bike ran perfect
during today's practice!
Why change it now?
If we mess with it now,
we'll never get that vehicle
working properly...
Personally, I think we
oughta deny that request!
Well, that may be true.
The person who sent this
request is an amateur,
who thinks we can win
the race simply by
increasing our
engine performance...
But, he's still
our valued sponsor,
and he's keeping
us in the race...
You understand that, right?
This project is going
to be an all-nighter...
so thank you in advance for
the hard work. That's all.
It's probably 'cause we
haven't won a single race...
Do you believe this crap?!
Jeez! Unbelievable!
Aw, man!
Well, I can't blame
them for being upset...
It takes sponsors
to have a team...
and money to win... Right?
Aaaahhh! I've had it!
Miss Chihiro?
Ah...
Hello. Good evening!
I guess I kinda... lost my cool.
Not at all...
This place is wonderful.
That's for sure!
When... I found out
I'd get to work here...
in a place like this...
I was just so excited...
I barely got any sleep.
I was working frantically.
And now I have the
fulfillment that comes from
being the head mechanic
everyone can depend on.
But it seems like
something's missing!
It seems...
I've been able to achieve
everything I ever wanted.
Do you think I'm spoiled?
Maybe this doesn't make
too much sense to you, huh?
As a matter of fact, it does.
I see the breeze that blows the
wind in your heart has shifted.
And it's no longer in harmony
with those around you.
Then, a gentle breeze
from your past blew in,
making you feel nostalgic,
and you were led back
to the Auto Club.
Lately, I can't stop
thinking about the past.
And when I returned to the
clubhouse after all that time,
there were people
like Morisato there.
That's why I decided...
that if I can race against
Morisato and win as I am now,
I'll be able to get over this...
And finally move on...
I mean, why not, right?
Does that seem like an
odd way of thinking to you?
Not at all... I understand it.
You really do
get it, don't you?
Yes. Because I am a goddess.
You sure are a funny one,
you know that?
As for Keiichi...
He will not be so
easily defeated.
The fact that I make
my living through racing
counts for something, too.
And I might have a few
tricks up my sleeve.
You can tell
Morisato I said that.
I'll tell him...
however, I doubt that Keiichi
will actually be
concerned about that.
Until we meet again.
Hey.
Are you in love with him?
With Morisato I mean.
I am!
Tamiya, Otaki...
I know you guys are in there.
You can come out now.
There you are. We've been
looking everywhere for you!
Since we missed you
back on campus,
we decided to come all the
way out here to see you!
Oh, so that's why you
guys are in there, huh?
Well, whatever...
You guys have managed to
round up a pretty good team...
Which is why I'm not planning to
hold back when I take them on.
You've done a good job.
Oh, thanks, Miss Chihiro...
You really are much too kind
to a couple of goons like us!
Oh, and one more thing...
There's the whole matter of
someone "modifying" my baby...
Uh, it was just that...
The auto club was
running low on funds,
we didn't have a choice!
No excuses.
Ugh!
We'll discuss this in full
detail later. So be prepared.
Please, Chihiro!
Have mercy! Don't be so cruel!
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
You're done already?
Yes.
Did Chihiro seem...
Yes?
Nevermind... I guess
it's all right.
Let's go home, huh?
Okay!
All right then...
The winner will be decided
after two laps around
the campus course.
Please take care to avoid
endangering pedestrians.
So, who do you think's
gonna win the race?
You nitwit...! It'll
obviously be Chihiro!
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
On your marks...
Get set...
GO!
Good luck to both of you.
But I do hope...
that Keiichi will win.
--Ah!
--Look out, you maniac!
Man, she's fast! How on earth
did she tune that thing?!
Hang in there! You still
have a long way to go!
I'm gonna win
this for Belldandy.
I'll have to give this
everything I've got.
Hm?
This way please!
Wasn't she just...
Right this way!
Uh... I'll figure
this out later.
Don't push it, Keiichi.
There's no way her engine can
possibly hold up at that speed.
I'll just keep a
nice steady pace.
And I'm sure my
chance will come!
Ah! Here they come!
--Go, Chihiro!
--Go, Chihiro! Yeah!
Not good. I guess it's time...
I don't see Keiichi anywhere...
Looks like he's
fallen way behind her.
Damn right he has!
He IS racing the
great Chihiro Fujimi!
Ah! There he is!
The distance between
him and Chihiro is...
Ah!
--It's Chihiro! She's stopped!
I guess her engine
couldn't hold up
at that constant high
rate of speed after all!
It doesn't make sense.
Chihiro should've known
that was going to happen...
Huh?!
It can't be! A spare engine!
No one ever said swapping in
a new engine was prohibited.
But still... She shouldn't be
able to achieve maximum speed
out of a newly swapped engine!
Those eyes...
They don't look at anything
but what lies straight ahead...
Just like mine used to do...
way back then...
--C'mon! Give it a good push!
--Heave-ho!
--Chihiro!
--Hm?
Come on, let's go get ready
for that big party tonight...
What're you doing?
Sorry, I can't... I'm too
busy here fixing this thing.
Huh...? But what're
you doing that for?
I guess it seemed
like it'd be fun!
Back in those days...
I can do it!
Here they come now!
And it looks like Keiichi's
finally out in front!
--He's WHAT?!
--Impossible!
Come on, Keiichi...
You can do it!
Uh?!
Chihiro?
I can make it!
You lost the race.
Yeah. But it's for the best,
don't you think?
After all, I'm not really the
one Chihiro was trying to beat.
So you realized that?
Yeah, somehow I did.
But still...
the message you
were able to convey
by racing with all your heart
did get through, Keiichi...
Just look.
--Hey, Morisato.
--Huh?
Thank you so much...
It was a very good race.
Thanks.
And it looked like you
were really enjoying it.
Yeah. I'd say you were, too.
Me...? You think so?
Uh-huh, and I thought
the same thing
when I watched you
repairing that old car.
I thought to myself,
"this is the kind of
person I'd like to race."
You wanted to race me?
Yeah! But then, you
were even more amazing
when you were racing
against me today.
The look on your face was
so serious and determined...
it was truly awesome.
Did... I say something funny?
Well, I guess it's true--great
minds really do think alike!
Huh?
Thanks again! And I owe
you some thanks also.
Thanks to you, I put
a lot of things behind me.
Oh, no... I really didn't
do anything for you at all.
Actually, it was all
thanks to Keiichi...
and to your own personal
strength as well, Miss Chihiro.
The two of you really
are... quite a pair!
Yes!
I see...
I really haven't changed...
since back then.
Whaaa-?! Chihiro says that...
she's going to quit her
job as head mechanic.
Huh?!
She says here that
it's because...
she wants to design
her own original bike
to be used for fun rather
than winning races.
Awesome...! I'd sure love
to try to do that, too!
As a matter of fact,
she also wrote that...
she knew you would say that.
Uh... She did, huh?
All right then...
Please explain what
makes you want to pursue
employment with our company.
Yes, sir!
There's something
I want to do here!
I had thought our relationship
was over long ago...
But as the plum trees
begin to blossom,
she remembers a love
from the past.
Next time, "Ah! A Goddess's
Tears and His Dream."
I'm telling you,
I'm NOT Urd's boyfriend!
Be sure to watch it!