♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
TO BLOW THIS SCENE, ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY AND
THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1,
LET'S JAM. ♪
MMM.
[BEEPING]
OH! A SHIP!
HI, I JUST PICKED UP
YOUR SIGNAL, AND, WELL,
I HAVE A SLIGHT PROBLEM.
I'M KINDA OUT OF
FUEL AT THE MOMENT.
SO, IF YOU COULD
JUST TAKE ME TO GANYMEDE,
I'D REALLY APPRECIATE... IT.
OH! AH, DAMMIT!
WHY IS EVERYONE IN SUCH
A HURRY ALL THE TIME?
DON'T THEY KNOW IT'S UNHEALTHY?
[BEEPING]
HMM?
HUH?
THE HOUSE SPECIALTY
IS SEA RAT.
USED TO BE A STAPLE FOOD
HARVESTED IN THE GANYMEDE SEA.
AFTER THE GATES STABILIZED,
FOOD WASN'T SCARCE ANYMORE,
AND PEOPLE STOPPED EATING IT.
SO, THEY RAN SOME
FANCY AD CAMPAIGNS
AND CLAIMED IT
WAS A DELICACY.
AND... IS IT TASTY?
IT'S TOTALLY DISGUSTING.
PEOPLE EAT IT ANYWAY
FOR STATUS... IT'S IN.
WELL, IN THAT CASE,
I GUESS I'M OUT.
LOBSTER MISO STEW, PLEASE.
ORDER ACCEPTED, ARIGATO.
WELL, I WANTED TO ORDER
THE MOST EXPENSIVE
THING ON THE MENU.
BECAUSE YOU THINK WHEN WE BAG
THIS GUY, WE'RE GONNA BE RICH?
[WHIRRING]
[LAUGHTER]
SO, GEMP IS A SPY, HUH?
BUT, MOM, THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT NOW.
WE BLEW HIS SHIP TO PIECES.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
ONE LOST AMPULE
DOESN'T MEAN MUCH.
WE'LL CONTINUE
AS WE INITIALLY PLANNED,
BUT WHEN THINGS GO WRONG,
SOMEONE MUST TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY, RIGHT?
[ALL GASP]
--M-MAMA?
--YOU, HARRISON?
UH...
UGH...
I DIDN'T! MOTHER!
HEY! WAITER!
WHERE'S MY SEA RAT SAUTEE?
HA HA HA!
C'MON, C'MON, DO THAT
MORPHIN FOR MY ENDORPHIN
YEAH, IT'S MORGAN.
IT'S A CLEAN MATCH.
SHOULD WE JUST GRAB HIM
AND FORGET ABOUT BREAKFAST?
YOUNG MAN, ARE YOU AWARE
THAT THE GANYMEDE SEA RAT
IS A VERY INTELLIGENT
AND KIND ANIMAL? HMM?
--WHAT'S THAT?
--THAT WOMAN... WHO IS SHE?
WELL, I DIDN'T KNOW
THE CIRCUS WAS IN TOWN!
[LAUGHTER]
MMM.
AAH!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
OH HAH!
I KNOW I'VE SEEN
THAT WOMAN BEFORE.
[JINGLE PLAYING]
ATTENTION. WE, THE SPACE
WARRIORS, ARE ECOSOLDIERS
WHO WORK NIGHT AND DAY
TO PRESERVE THE ENVIRONMENT
AND PROTECT ENDANGERED SPECIES
ALL OVER THE UNIVERSE.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR COOPERATION.
I REMEMBER! THAT WOMAN
HAS A 25 MILLION BOUNTY!
HUH?
[DING]
MOM! HURRY!
STOP RIGHT THERE.
GAME OVER.
--MOM!
TAKE IT EASY.
YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE
YOUR DEAR MOTHER HURT NOW.
YOU BETTER LET HER GO!
HOW'S OUR BOY MORGAN?
UGH, HE'S ALL FULL OF HOLES.
THANKS TO YOU,
WE LOST OUR REWARD.
FORTUNATELY, YOU'RE
WORTH A LOT MORE.
25 MILLION WILL BUY
A LOT OF LOBSTER STEW.
OH, IF YOU HURT HER,
WE'RE GONNA TEAR--
HOLD YOUR FIRE!
THESE MEN ARE PROFESSIONAL
BOUNTY HUNTERS.
THERE'S NOTHING
WE CAN DO FOR NOW.
MOM! TAKE CARE OF
THE BASE WHILE I'M AWAY.
--I'LL BE BACK IN NO TIME.
--BETTER HIT THE ROAD, RAT BOYS.
I DON'T THINK YOU WANNA BE
HERE WHEN THE POLICE SHOW UP.
--HANG IN THERE, MOM.
--OH, HARRISON.
YOU'LL GET YOUR PUNISHMENT
LATER WHEN I RETURN.
--MOTHER!
--UGH! AAH!
IT'S HARRISON'S LUCKY DAY.
MAMA WON'T BE BACK FOR A WHILE.
--HEY, YOU, ARE YOU ALIVE?
--UGH...
--TAKE THIS TO THE I.S.S.P.
--HUH?
BUT DON'T...
DON'T OPEN THE CASE.
--AH!
--OH, NO!
--UNH.
--HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO WITH THIS THING?
UNIVERSAL ENVIRONMENTAL
PROTECTION SOCIETY?
MORE LIKE
ENVIRONMENTAL TERRORISTS.
THEY'RE CALLED
"THE SPACE WARRIORS."
USED TO BE A GOOD GROUP
OF DEDICATED PEOPLE
WORKING TO PRESERVE
THE ENVIRONMENT
AND PROTECT ENDANGERED SPECIES.
THEY DID GREAT WORK
ALL AROUND THE ASTEROIDS.
BUT A FEW YEARS AGO, A NEW
LEADER TOOK OVER THE GROUP,
AND EVERYTHING CHANGED.
MOST OF THE MEMBERS
DROPPED OUT.
THOSE WHO WERE LEFT
ARE MORE VIOLENT
THAN THE LOCAL
CRIME SYNDICATES.
THEY HAVE A SPECIAL THING
FOR THE GANYMEDE SEA RATS.
AND GUESS WHO'S IN CHARGE
OF THESE PSYCHO TERRORISTS?
"TWINKLE" MARIA MURDOCH.
PLEASE DO NOT ASSOCIATE
US WITH COMMON TERRORISTS.
WE ARE WARRIORS OF PEACE,
FIGHTING A NOBLE BATTLE
FOR THE LAW
OF NATURE.
YEAH, YEAH. WE SAW
HOW PEACEFUL YOU ARE.
NOW, HOW DO WE
PICK UP THAT REWARD?
THE GANYMEDE POLICE.
BUT THE GOVERNMENT
JUST BLOCKED IT.
--UNH!
--WHAT?
I'M TRYING TO TRACK IT.
LOOKS LIKE THE GOVERNMENT
CANCELLED THEIR
OFFER AS OF YESTERDAY.
WHY'D THEY DO THAT?
HEE HEE HEE.
WHEN YOU'RE TOLD NOT TO OPEN
SOMETHING, WELL, WHO CAN RESIST?
OH, NOW, I DIDN'T REALLY
OPEN THIS THING, YOU KNOW?
IT JUST OPENED UP BY ITSELF.
HMM.
OH!
AH HA.
[SCREAMING]
READY. WE FOLLOWED
YOUR INSTRUCTIONS.
THE BOUNTY'S BEEN CANCELLED.
WE ALSO HAVE
A BILL THAT WILL
PROTECT THE SEA RATS
FROM HARVESTING.
THE SEA RATS ON GANYMEDE
WILL BE SAFE.
--MMM.
--WHERE IS MOM?
WELL, WHOEVER'S GOT HER
HASN'T CONTACTED US YET,
BUT WE'RE TRYING
TO TRACK THEM DOWN.
IF WE CATCH THEM,
I PROMISE YOU WE'LL, UH...
IF MOM ISN'T BACK HERE
SOON, AND I MEAN SOON,
WE'LL SET THE PLAN
IN MOTION IMMEDIATELY.
WAIT! WE'RE TRYING TO DO
EVERYTHING YOU ASKED FOR.
WE'RE CARRYING OUT YOUR WISHES.
[SQUEAK SQUEAK]
[SCREAMING]
HMM.
WHATEVER IT IS, YOU CAN'T
EAT IT, AND I'M STARVING!
[BEEPING]
HUH? AH!
LOOK AT THIS.
THERE'S NO RECORD OF THAT
TERRORIST ATTACK WE SAW.
--MAN, WHAT IS GOING ON?
--HEE HEE HEE.
I TOLD YOU YOU WERE
WASTING YOUR TIME.
YOU MUST FEEL VERY FOOLISH.
MIGHT AS WELL
LET ME GO. YOU'VE LOST.
NOT QUITE. THERE'S
SOMETHING BEHIND ALL THIS.
[BEEPING]
HI, I JUST
PICKED UP YOUR SIGNAL,
AND WELL, I HAVE
A SLIGHT PROBLEM.
I'M KIND OF OUT
OF FUEL AT THE MOMENT.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
IF YOU COULD JUST
TAKE ME TO GANYMEDE,
I'D BE VERY APPRECIATIVE.
UNH. PLEASE?
OR IF YOU COULD JUST
LOAN ME A SPARE FUEL ROD,
I'D PAY YOU BACK, OF COURSE.
--UGH.
--ARE YOU LISTENING?
I KNOW YOU'RE THERE!
SAY SOMETHING!
HUH?
[BONK]
OW!
UGH!
THAT'S WHAT YOU DID?
YOU TOOK ALL THE MONEY
YOU STOLE FROM US,
AND YOU LOST IT
GAMBLING AT A CASINO?
YOU KNOW WHAT
THEY SAY, COWBOY,
"EASY COME, EASY GO."
THEY ALSO SAY THERE'S
NO HONOR AMONG THIEVES.
GOT ANYTHING, JET?
NAH. I HAVE
AN OLD FRIEND ON GANYMEDE.
I'M TRYING TO REACH HIM.
AW, MAN. THERE'S NOTHING
EVEN WORTH SALVAGING.
HUH? WHAT'S THIS?
OH!
NO, WE STILL DON'T KNOW
WHERE THE VIRUS IS.
YES, MR. PRESIDENT.
WE'LL DO OUR BEST.
--OH!
--HEY, CHIEF!
WHAT?
IT'S ABOUT THE MEN WHO
KIDNAPPED TWINKLE MURDOCH.
DID YOU FIND THEM YET?
UGH... AND YOU'RE SURE
THIS GUY TOLD YOU
TO TAKE THIS
TO THE I. S. S. P.?
YES, AND I'M SURE
THAT THING'S WORTH A LOT.
SO , LET'S SAY WE CALL IT EVEN,
AND YOU CUT ME LOOSE.
RIGHT, FAYE, LIKE I'M GONNA
TAKE YOUR WORD FOR THIS.
WHAT? UH, WHAT'S THIS
WHOLE THING ABOUT, BOB?
IT'S NO BIG THING, JET.
THEY DECIDED TO CANCEL
THE BOUNTY OFFER.
YOU'D BETTER LET HER GO,
OR THEY'LL BOOK YOU
FOR KIDNAPPING.
NO, BOB.
YOU KNOW, WHEN WE WORKED
IN THE SAME DEPARTMENT,
A LOT OF THOSE ILLEGAL EYEDROPS
WE PICKED UP SEEMED
TO DISAPPEAR.
WAIT A MINUTE!
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING, JET?
IF YOU WANT TO WORK
UNTIL RETIREMENT AGE,
KIND OF A BAD IDEA TO TURN
AGAINST ME NOW, OLD BUDDY.
ALL RIGHT.
I GET YOUR MESSAGE, JET.
SO, WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO KNOW?
[GRUNTING]
HEY! DON'T
BREAK THE THING!
SHH!
THEY CALL IT NEGOTIATIONS,
BUT THEY'RE THREATENING
TO UNLEASH A NEW VIRUS.
IN EFFECT, ALL 8 MILLION PEOPLE
ON GANYMEDE ARE THEIR HOSTAGES.
HOW'D THEY PULL IT OFF?
THEY SHANGHAIED A BIOENGINEER,
RETRO VIRUS SPECIALIST,
FORCED HIM TO DESIGN
A VIRUS TO THEIR SPECS.
IT'S CALLED "MONKEY BUSINESS."
IT SEEMS HUMANS AND MONKEYS
HAVE ONLY A 2% DIFFERENCE
IN THEIR D.N.A. STRUCTURE.
THIS VIRUS IS TWEAKED TO ACT
JUST ON THE 2%.
SO, IT WON'T HAVE AN EFFECT
ON ANY OTHER ANIMALS OR PLANTS.
IT'LL LEAVE THE REST
OF THE ECOSYSTEM INTACT.
--HUH?
--THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S UNIQUELY SELECTIVE.
YOU SEE, IT ONLY SEEKS
OUT HUMAN BEINGS.
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
YOU DON'T GIVE UP, DO YOU?
I.S.S.P. HAD A MOLE
INSIDE THEIR GROUP,
BUT WE LOST CONTACT WITH HIM.
HE MAY BE DEAD,
SO WE HAD NO OTHER OPTION.
SO, YOU'RE GONNA CAVE IN,
EVEN THOUGH WE'VE GOT
THE LEADER OF
THE WHOLE GROUP HERE?
WE'RE HOLDING THE TRUMP CARD
RIGHT HERE IN OUR HANDS!
ORDERS FROM THE TOP!
THERE'S NOTHING THAT WE CAN DO!
OH!
WE'RE LETTING HER GO.
HA HA HA!
[CLANG]
US OR THEM WHICH ONE?
WHICH ONE OF US TRULY DESERVES
PUNISHMENT FROM HEAVEN?
SOON, THE HOUR OF JUDGMENT
WILL ARRIVE.
YES, VERY SOON.
THE RELEASE PROCEDURE
IS COMPLETE.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO TRACK HER
USING OUR COVERT AGENTS.
AND THE SATELLITE?
IT'LL BE OPERATIONAL
IN ABOUT AN HOUR.
GET THE TECH TEAM READY.
BUT DON'T TAKE ACTION
TILL WE KNOW THE LOCATION
OF THE VIRUS!
SIR! A COMMUNICATION
FROM TWINKLE MURDOCH!
HUH?
LONG TIME, NO SEE,
EH, MINISTER?
NOW, ABOUT ALL THOSE
PROMISES YOU MADE.
WELL, YES.
WE'VE PASSED A BILL TO LIMIT
THE HARVESTING OF THE SEA RATS,
SO THEIR POPULATION WILL
BE MAINTAINED SECURELY.
I DIDN'T SAY "LIMIT;"
I SAID "PROHIBIT."
WELL, THEN, I'LL BRING IT
BACK UP IN THE PARLIAMENT...
TO LOOK AT IT
IN A POSITIVE LIGHT.
MMHMM.
I THINK YOU NEED A DEMONSTRATION
OF WHAT'S IN STORE FOR YOU.
WAIT! WE CAN DISCUSS THIS!
MOTHER! PLEASE! NOT THIS!
MOTHER, PLEASE! NO!
[GROWLS]
[WHINES]
ALPHA 105, TEAM LEADER.
TARGET HAS ENTERED
THE WASTELAND SECTOR.
[STATIC]
ACKNOWLEDGED.
CONTINUE PURSUIT.
[BEEPING]
HUH?
[EXPLOSIONS]
TAH! IS THAT
ALL THEY WERE PLANNING?
[CRUNCH]
OH, DAMN!
ALL THAT WORK AND NO REWARD.
[BEEPING]
JET! CAN YOU HEAR ME?
TUNE INTO FREQUENCY 72 NOW!
HUH?
THEY'RE DOING A LIVE BROADCAST
FROM THEIR OWN SATELLITE!
THIS IS NO LONGER
ABOUT SEA RATS ON GANYMEDE.
HUMANS WITH THEIR CONSUMER
CULTURE HAVE ESCAPED
FROM THE VAST SYSTEM
THAT WE CALL NATURE
AND ARE COMMITTING CRIMES
THAT CANNOT BE AMENDED.
THOSE WHO ARE UNAWARE OF THIS
ARE WHAT YOU MIGHT
CALL "GLITCHES"
IN THE NATURAL SYSTEM,
OR TO PUT IT SIMPLY, "BUGS."
THEY WEREN'T THERE!
THAT SHIP WAS A DECOY!
WHERE ARE THEY
BROADCASTING FROM?
THEY'RE NOT VERY FAR.
THERE, I GOT IT!
THEY'RE IN HYPERSPACE!
OUR RETROVIRUS,
MONKEY BUSINESS,
TAKES THESE RETROHUMANS
AND RETURNS THEM TO THEIR
PROPER PLACE IN NATURE.
NOW, DO YOU UNDERSTAND, HUH?
AU REVOIR.
GOOD NEWS, JET.
THE GANYMEDE GOVERNMENT
JUST RENEWED THE RANSOM
ON TWINKLE AND HER GROUP.
--OH, YEAH?
--THIS IS IT!
WE'RE CLOSE ENOUGH
TO GET TO THEM,
AND THERE'S NO
ONE TO INTERFERE.
I'M AFRAID THAT JUST CATCHING
THEM WON'T BE GOOD ENOUGH.
HUH?
IF THOSE MISSILES
HIT GANYMEDE,
THERE'LL BE NO ONE LEFT TO PAY
YOUR BOUNTY EXCEPT MONKEYS.
[HUMMING]
ARF! ARF!
SO, NO ONE'S GONNA
BITCH IF WE GET RID OF
THAT MONKEY
MISSILE NOW, RIGHT?
YEAH, BUT THERE'S NOT MUCH TIME.
THEY'RE AT ONE
OF THE GATE EXITS.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT IT.
ORDER UP THE DEFENSE SYSTEM!
4 MINUTES 30 SECONDS TO IMPACT.
THE SYSTEM WON'T BE READY!
HURRY! THIS IS AN EMERGENCY!
GET THE PRESIDENT ON THE LINE!
THEY'RE RIGHT UP AHEAD.
OH, SHIT! IT SPLIT!
JET! I GOT TWO!
LOCK ON THE OTHER ONE!
WHAT? THERE ARE
NO WEAPONS ONLINE.
THAT MISSILE
WILL HIT GANYMEDE
BEFORE I HAVE
A CHANCE TO RECHARGE.
HEY THERE, HAVING
A LITTLE TROUBLE?
--HUH?
--I CAN BAIL YOU OUT FOR 80%.
--YOU'RE INSANE!
--OK!
BYE-BYE NOW!
ALL RIGHT! 40%!
THAT'S MY LAST OFFER!
--OK, I GET THE 60!
--DEAL!
JUST DO IT!
DAMN! THERE'S NO TIME LEFT!
COME ON!
--OH!
--WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S MULTIPLE WARHEADS!
AND THIS IS NOT THE MILITARY!
♪ I'LL MAKE MONKEYS
OUT OF YOU ALL ♪
JET, LISTEN!
TOP BRASS ARE GONNA
CLOSE UP THE STARGATE.
--WHAT?
--THEY'RE GOING TO ENCLOSE
THE WHOLE THING
IN HYPERSPACE.
--MISSILES AND ALL!
--THIS IS NO JOKE!
SPIKE!
GRR! I HEAR YOU!
GO, SPIKE!
UNH!
WHEW.
HMM? HUH?
WHAT'S THAT?
--AAH!
--OHH!
UNH...
DIDN'T YOU PAY ATTENTION IN
YOUR HIGH SCHOOL PHYSICS CLASS?
MATTER THAT GETS
ENCLOSED IN HYPERSPACE
CAN BE VIEWED
NORMALLY BY THE NAKED EYE.
BUT OF COURSE,
IT CAN NEVER INTERACT
WITH THE MATTER ON
THIS PLANE OF REALITY.
MOM! THE GATE'S CLOSED!
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO, MAMA?
STOP! STOP!
UNH!
UGH... UGH...
AH...
OH!
YEAH, YEAH, ALL THAT
WORK AND NO REWARD.
FOR TOUGH GUYS,
YOU SURE COMPLAIN A LOT.
NOW, DON'T TAKE IT
SO HARD, BOYS.
WE'LL MAKE SOME BIG
BUCKS ON THE NEXT ONE.
WELL, I THINK I'LL GO
TAKE A SHOWER NOW.
[HUMMING]
NEXT TIME?
"WE'LL" MAKE MONEY?
JET, IS SHE SAYING
WHAT I THINK SHE'S SAYING?
'CAUSE IF SHE IS--
I DON'T KNOW, AND
I HAVE NO OPINION.
MAN... SHE'S TAKING
A SHOWER IN OUR SHOWER.
THAT'S NOT OK, RIGHT?
DON'T KNOW.
HAVE NO OPINION.
FINE. I'LL GO
TELL HER MYSELF.
HMM.
HUH-- WAIT, SPIKE!
[BANG BANG]
BAD MOVE, SPIKEO.
THE MUSIC BOX IS BROKEN...
OR IS IT?
IT STARTS TO PLAY, AND A
HAUNTING TUNE FILLS THE AIR.
I AWAKE SUDDENLY FROM MY DREAM.
THERE IS NO MUSIC BOX!
AND YET, THERE IT IS
A TINY ONE,
NESTLED IN MY HAND.
AND I AWAKE FROM MY DREAM AGAIN,
AS IF I WERE PEELING AN ONION,
IT'S A DREAM
NO MATTER HOW FAR I GO.
I CAN NEVER REACH REALITY.
TRAPPED IN AN ENDLESS NIGHTMARE.
NEXT EPISODE,
BALLAD FOR FALLEN ANGELS.