♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1,
LET'S JAM ♪
[HARMONICA PLAYING]
[BUBBLING]
AAH!
[PANTING]
[HARMONICA PLAYING]
HMM.
[DOG WHINES AND BARKS]
[PANTING]
[CHUCKLES]
[DOG WHINING]
UM!
[PANTING]
IF YOU DON'T WORK,
YOU DON'T EAT.
YOU'RE A HUNTING DOG.
HUNT UP SOME FOOD.
WE GIRLS ARE DIFFERENT.
WE HAVE TO BE PAMPERED BECAUSE
WE'RE DELICATE AND REFINED.
[SLURPING]
MMMMM.
HMM.
3 MILLION WOOLONG REWARD?
WELL, I'LL JUST HAVE
THE BOYS GET IT FOR ME, THEN.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
DAMN, THAT BLUES
HARP SOUNDS SWEET.
I KNEW IT WOULD.
HMM! I THOUGHT
YOU LIKED JAZZ.
DON'T BE DENSE.
I STARTED WAILING THE BLUES
WHEN THE DOCTOR
WHACKED MY BOTTOM
ON THE DAY I WAS BORN.
A BABY HIPSTER... VERY COOL.
[BEEPING]
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT,
IT'S GIRAFFE.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING IN FROM THE RIGHT.
YOU TAKE THE LEFT SIDE.
LARD BOY IS IN THE WAY.
HMM? OH!
THAT'S FATTY.
MAKE A MOVE, JET.
THE BALL'S IN YOUR COURT.
HMM.
YO! HEY, FATTY!
--HUH?
--FATTY RIVER!
--LONG TIME NO SEE, BUDDY!
--OH! WHO'D HAVE GUESSED?
IF IT ISN'T JET BLACK.
WELL, WELL. WHEN THE HELL
DID YOU BLOW IN?
HOW ABOUT YOU?
YOU'RE LOOKING PRETTY CHEERY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
DID YOU CATCH A NICE BIG ONE?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
I HAD NO IDEA YOU WERE
A FAN OF THE BLUES, FATTY.
YOU KIDDING ME?
I LISTENED TO THE BLUES
WHEN I WAS STILL
IN MY FATHER'S SACK,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[NO AUDIO]
UNH!
UH, SORRY.
HEY!
[DING]
[TONE SOUNDS]
HMPH!
GIVE IT BACK NOW!
ZEBRA!
YAAH!
[GASPS]
HEY, YOU! WAKE UP!
HEY!
AW, GREAT.
YOU DIE, AND I LOSE THE REWARD.
DON'T... DON'T
BE FOOLED BY HIM...
BY THE WAY HE LOOKS.
DON'T TALK!
TRY TO STAY ALIVE!
NOT ME.
HE NEEDS HELP NOW.
HELP HIM.
THIS STONE...
[SIRENS WAILING]
WAIT!
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
[BEEP]
[BEEPING]
HMM.
I CAN'T BE SURE
UNTIL I RUN ALL THE TESTS,
BUT THIS MAY BE WORTH
A HEFTY SUM.
SO WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO DO WITH IT?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
THE GUY GIVES IT
TO ME ON HIS OWN,
THEN HE DIES ON HIS OWN.
I DON'T SEE ANY REASON
WHY WE SHOULDN'T KEEP IT.
THERE IS NO REASON.
YOU'RE NOT RESPONSIBLE
FOR THAT KID, AFTER ALL.
GIVE ME THAT!
HMM.
THIS THING IS GOING
TO PAY FOR OUR FOOD.
OUR FOOD, NOT YOURS.
YOU KNOW, I THINK YOUR
HEART'S MADE OUT OF LEAD.
NOT LIKE ME.
I'M A NICE GUY.
I HAVE A GIFT FOR YOU.
YAY!
ALL RIGHT, WHAT IS IT?
AN OFFICIAL INVOICE?
AN INVOICE FOR WHAT?
ALL THE EXPENSES
YOU'VE RACKED UP
SINCE YOU'VE BEEN ON OUR SHIP.
AND THANKS FOR YOUR BUSINESS.
YEAH. GREAT. ANYTIME.
WHY DO YOU WANT
TO KNOW ABOUT THIS DEAD GUY?
WELL, UH...
HA! SO YOU WERE
AFTER GIRAFFE, TOO.
DID YOU GET A GOOD DEAL?
HMM?
[CHUCKLES]
ENJOYING THE SWEETS?
I ALWAYS DO.
THERE'S NO BOUNTY IN IT,
YOU KNOW.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THERE'S NOTHING TO
GAIN HERE AT ALL.
HMM.
NO, I MEAN IT.
THERE'S NOTHING
ON THE LINE HERE.
YEAH, RIGHT, JET.
YOU'RE GOING TO OWE
ME ONE FOR TODAY.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW THAT KID
ON THE BLUES HARP
THE OTHER DAY? NAME'S WEN.
GIRAFFE WAS AFTER
THE KID'S SO-CALLED FATHER,
AN OLD FRIEND.
HE GOES BY THE NAME ZEBRA.
THEY WERE FRIENDS?
SHEESH!
YOU DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THAT?
THE TWO OF THEM WERE THE LEADERS
OF THE SELF-DEFENSE
VOLUNTEER SQUAD.
THEY WORKED TOGETHER
UNTIL ABOUT 10 YEARS AGO.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHY WAS HE AFTER AN OLD COMRADE?
[HARMONICA PLAYING]
10 YEARS AGO,
THEY HAD A CONFRONTATION
WITH SOME SPACE RAIDERS
A LAND DISPUTE.
IT ALL CAME DOWN AT SOME
R&amp;D FACILITY NEAR MARS.
A FEW DAYS LATER,
THE RAIDERS ARE WIPED OUT,
ZEBRA IS MISSING,
AND GIRAFFE IS FOUND
BLINDFOLDED IN A SILO.
THEY SAY ZEBRA
DOUBLE-CROSSED HIM
SO HE COULD RUN THE SQUAD SOLO.
LATER, ZEBRA TURNS UP
IN A WHEELCHAIR WITH THE KID.
GUESS IT DIDN'T TURN OUT
THE WAY HE PLANNED.
[HARMONICA PLAYING]
SO THE BOTTOM LINE IS,
GIRAFFE WAS KILLED OFF
OVER SOME INTERNAL POLITICS.
BETRAYAL MAY COME
EASILY TO WOMEN,
BUT MEN LIVE BY
IRON CODES OF HONOR.
YOU BELIEVE THAT?
I'M TRYING TO, REAL HARD.
[HARMONICA PLAYING]
[HARMONICA STOPS]
TELL ME... WHO ARE YOU?
JUST SOME SUSPICIOUS GUY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT HERE?
BEFORE GIRAFFE
BOUGHT THE FARM,
HE ASKED ME TO COME
HERE TO HELP YOU.
BUT ZEBRA SHOT GIRAFFE.
UHHUH.
THEN WHY WOULD GIRAFFE
ASK HIM TO HELP THE KID?
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
HMM? HEY, THE KID'S
IN THE HEADLINES.
GUESS HE MUST BE
PRETTY FAMOUS, HUH?
YEAH.
KID'S A GENIUS.
PLAYS LIKE AN OLD PRO.
HMM?
[GASPS]
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
THIS GUY ISN'T ZEBRA.
WHAT'S THAT?
LOOK CLOSE.
CAN'T YOU SEE THE DATE?
WHAT THE HELL?!
THIS WAS PUBLISHED 30 YEARS AGO.
HOW CAN HE HAVE THE SAME FACE?
COME ON.
THERE'S NOTHING TO BE AFRAID OF.
COME HERE. LET'S TALK.
[GUNSHOT]
UNH!
YOU'D BETTER STAY OUT OF IT.
HUH?
LITTLE TWERP LIKE YOU
STICKS HIS NECK OUT TOO FAR,
HE'LL GET IT CUT OFF.
UNDERSTAND?
AAH!
DON'T GIVE ME THAT CRAP, KID!
SORRY, BUT I'M NOT A KID.
YEAH.
ALL KIDS SAY THAT.
I KNOW WHAT I LOOK LIKE,
BUT I WAS ALIVE
WHEN THIS PLACE WAS AN OUTPOST,
BEFORE THE ASTEROIDS
WERE EVEN SETTLED.
GET THE PICTURE?
[BLUES HARMONICA PLAYING]
[RUMBLING]
[THUNDER]
THE HYPERSPACE GATE
HAD BLOWN TO BITS.
FROM THAT DAY ON, MY BODY
COMPLETELY STOPPED AGING.
I CAN'T DIE.
THERE WAS ALWAYS
SOMEONE DISCOVERING ME,
DOING EXPERIMENTS,
BUT THEY ALL DIED,
AND I KEPT ON LIVING.
THE END FOR THIS GUY STARTED
WHEN HIS SELF-DEFENSE
VOLUNTEER SQUAD HIT OUR R&amp;D LAB.
I NEEDED A NEW COVER,
SOMEONE TO PLAY
THE PART OF MY PARENT.
DON'T... DON'T
BE FOOLED BY HIM...
BY THE WAY HE LOOKS.
NOT ME.
HE NEEDS HELP NOW.
HELP HIM.
I THINK HE'S THE THIRD GUY
I'VE USED LIKE THIS.
NOW, WHERE'S THE RING?
RING?
WHAT RING?
[GUNSHOT]
UNH!
THAT'S OK.
EVEN IF YOU HAD IT,
IT'D JUST BE A CASE OF
CASTING PEARLS BEFORE SWINE.
[COCKS GUN]
UNH!
[GUNFIRE]
[RELOADS GUN]
[GUNSHOT]
UNH!
[GUN CLATTERS TO FLOOR]
[GUNSHOT]
UNH!
[GUNFIRE]
AAH!
[CRASH]
AW, QUIT COMPLAINING,
YOU BIG KLUTZ.
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU GOT AWAY WITH
THIS LITTLE SCRATCH ON YOUR ARM.
BUT WE DON'T HAVE THE MONEY
TO PAY FOR A FUNERAL.
I'M SORRY.
HMM?
HMM.
[DOG BARKING]
CAN IT, EIN!
DON'T BE OBNOXIOUS.
[DOG WHINING]
HUH?
HMM?
JET... THE ALPHACATCH.
[BEEPING]
AW, CRAP.
THIS PIECE OF JUNK!
ALL RIGHT.
NOW... WHAT DO YOU
MAKE OUT OF THIS?
A HOTEL ROOM. THAT'S IT.
HE'S REMEMBERING THE TIME
GIRAFFE GOT BLOWN AWAY.
GIVE IT BACK NOW!
ZEBRA, COME OVER HERE! HURRY!
DAMN.
AND THEN WHAT?
COME ON, WHAT DID GIRAFFE SAY?
I HAVE IT NOW.
I CAN DO YOU IN WITH THIS.
THIS STONE HAS THE POWER
TO RETURN TIME TO YOU.
NOW, HAND ZEBRA OVER TO ME!
ZEBRA!
[GUNSHOT]
[BLUES HARMONICA PLAYING]
WHEN THE GATE EXPLODED,
A COORDINATE SYSTEM WAS CREATED
FROM THE RESULTING
TWISTS IN HYPERSPACE
A KIND OF SINGULARITY THAT
DREW IN VAST AMOUNTS OF ENERGY,
ENCLOSING AND CRYSTALLIZING
THEM INTO A SINGLE-FACETED STONE
THE GEM THAT MAKES UP THIS RING.
THE SAME ENERGY BROKE
WEN'S CIRCADIAN RHYTHM.
HIS PINEAL BODY
CONTINUALLY PRODUCES
A SUBSTANCE LIKE MELATONIN
THAT INHIBITS AGING.
THAT'S THE THEORY IN A NUTSHELL.
GET THE PICTURE?
YEAH, AS IF.
HMM.
I DON'T, EITHER,
WHICH SIMPLY MEANS...
THERE'S NO WAY TO KNOW FOR SURE
UNTIL WE STICK THE GEM
INTO THE KID AND FIND OUT.
ANYTHING COULD HAPPEN.
IT COULD BLOW SKYHIGH
THE MOMENT IT HITS.
KIND OF MAKES IT INTERESTING.
YES, MY DEAR?
I JUST THOUGHT
I'D SAY GOODBYE, SPIKE,
SINCE I'M SURE IT'S THE LAST
TIME I'LL BE SEEING YOU.
HUH! YOU MEAN,
YOU'RE FINALLY LEAVING US?
NO! I MEAN YOU'RE
NOT COMING BACK.
[FLICKS LIGHTER]
[CLICK]
I DON'T LIKE THIS SETUP, JET.
DON'T LIKE IT AT ALL.
MEN ARE SUCH TOTAL IDIOTS.
[GUNSHOT]
[WINDOW SHATTERS]
[DOG BARKING]
[GUNFIRE]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GUNSHOT]
[GASPS]
[GASPING AND MOANING]
UH, UH...
I SEE.
YES, I CAN FINALLY DIE AT LAST.
UH, I FEEL SO HEAVY...
UH... BUT I FEEL
I FINALLY FEEL AT EASE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
DO YOU UNDERSTAND? DO YOU?
[BLOWS INTO HARMONICA]
YEAH, I UNDERSTAND.
AS IF.
BANG.
[MAN SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
[SPEECH INAUDIBLE
OVER LOUD ROCK MUSIC]
YOU KNOW WHAT
HEAVY METAL IS, RIGHT?
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
HEAVY METAL!
I SAID, HEAVY METAL!
WHAT?!
I CAN'T HEAR YOU!
HEY! CAN YOU DO SOMETHING
ABOUT ALL THAT NOISE?
IT'S GOING TO BE RUNNING
THROUGH THE WHOLE NEXT EPISODE.
I THINK I'LL STAY
OUT OF IT, THEN!
I CAN'T HEAR A WORD
YOU'RE SAYING!
NEXT EPISODE
HEAVY METAL QUEEN!
IS THIS REALLY
GETTING THROUGH TO ANYONE?