♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1,
LET'S JAM ♪
YOUR ATTENTION, PLEASE.
WE WILL SOON BE
ARRIVING ON VENUS.
ALL PASSENGERS,
PLEASE BE AWARE
OF THE FOLLOWING
GOVERNMENT HEALTH ADVISORY.
THE FLOATING PLANTS
USED FOR TERRAFORMING ON VENUS
MAY CAUSE AN ALLERGIC
REACTION IN SOME PEOPLE.
IF UNTREATED, THIS CONDITION
CAN LEAD TO VENUS SICKNESS,
A POTENTIALLY FATAL ILLNESS.
THEREFORE, IF SYMPTOMS APPEAR,
PLEASE CONSULT
A DOCTOR IMMEDIATELY.
[WATCHES BEEPING]
[MACHINE GUN FIRE]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
EVERYBODY, QUIET DOWN!
BOTH HANDS BEHIND YOUR HEAD!
ALL OF YOU!
I-I'LL GIVE YOU MONEY!
TAKE THE OTHERS,
BUT LET ME GO, PLEASE!
HURRY, OR YOU'LL GET THE SAME.
DAMN IT. WHY DID THIS
HAVE TO BE THE DAY?
YOU OVER THERE!
HEY!
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
YOU, GET UP!
ALL RIGHT, PUT YOUR HANDS BEHIND
YOUR HEAD LIKE EVERYONE ELSE!
HEY, LOOK AT ME!
DON'T YOU GO BACK
TO SLEEP, YOU LITTLE-- AAH!
[YAWNING]
YOU'RE DEAD!
--HUH?
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
DON'T MOVE! HUH?
THINK AGAIN,
MY PRECIOUS BOUNTY HEADS.
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
THAT'S 5,000 WOOLONGS!
I HAD TO CHARGE
YOU OUR SPECIAL RATE.
SPECIAL RATE? THAT'S
NOT WRITTEN DOWN ANYWHERE!
YOU'RE SENDING THIS TO A SPECIAL
LOCATION, NOT A RESIDENCE.
ALL RIGHT. THEN COULD
YOU DO THIS FOR ME?
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE DESERT,
I'M AFRAID
THAT'S OUR BEST PRICE.
YOU KNOW,
YOUR BEST PRICE SUCKS.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO.
MAKE SURE IT
GETS THERE, OR ELSE.
HEY, WAIT!
THANKS FOR THE PAYOFF.
HI.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
MY SHARE.
RIGHT HERE?
WHY NOT? I NEED IT NOW.
HUH? AHA!
THAT'S ALL YOU'RE
GONNA GET, FAYE.
I KNOW. DON'T SWEAT IT.
DEPOSITING IT
AT THE CASINO AGAIN?
IT'S A LOT MORE
FUN THAN THE BANK.
HUH. GIRL NEVER GIVES UP.
I REALLY HATE DEALING
WITH PICKPOCKETS.
[LAUGHING]
AMAZING.
YOU REALLY ARE AMAZING.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE THE GUY
WHO FRAGGED THOSE HIJACKERS.
YOU HAVE SOME VERY
SMOOTH MOVES, MY FRIEND.
CAN I ASK YOU A FAVOR?
CAN YOU TEACH A GUY LIKE ME HOW
TO MAKE ALL THOSE COOL MOVES,
LIKE JUDO AND KUNG FU?
WHOOOO!
HUH?
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
I WANT TO BE A TOUGH
GUY LIKE YOU, YOU KNOW?
YOU ARE REALLY ANNOYING.
NOW, WHAT PART OF "NO"
DIDN'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
OH, COME ON.
I CAN DO IT.
JUST GIVE ME A TRY.
I BEG YOU, MASTER.
GOING DOWN.
HUH? WAIT A SECOND.
WHAT WAS THAT GUY'S STORY?
[BELL RINGS]
HMM?
[PANTING]
HUH?
COME ON.
JUST A FEW MOVES.
THINK OF IT AS HELPING ME,
YOU KNOW, LIKE SHOWING
A LITTLE MERCY AND COMPASSION.
AFRAID I'M FRESH
OUT OF THAT STUFF.
HAVE A HEART, MASTER. COME ON.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT REALLY
COSTS YOU ANYTHING.
[SQUEAKY VOICE]
GIVE IT UP, ALREADY.
VENUS HAS A LOT OF HELIUM
IN THE ATMOSPHERE.
YOU CAN FIX IT WITH THESE
LITTLE POPPER PILLS.
[GROANS]
HUH? COME ON!
THAT'S NOT FAIR!
[SQUEAKY VOICE]
YOU BROUGHT IT ON YOURSELF.
[LAUGHS]
THOSE WERE JUST
REGULAR THROAT DROPS.
YOU'RE PUSHING IT!
OH, HANDS-ON TRAINING.
WHOO! WAH!
HEEYAH! OOHWAH!
YOU'RE, UH--
THE NAME IS ROCO BONNARO.
IT'S AN HONOR, MASTER.
FIRST REWARD WE'VE
PICKED UP IN A LONG TIME.
SO I GOT SOME TASTY
DOG FOOD FOR YOU.
THIS IS ALL THANKS
TO THE BRILLIANT MASTERMIND.
NOW, LET'S SEE WHO'S UP NEXT.
I'M TELLING YOU,
DON'T TENSE UP.
HOW AM I GONNA KNOCK
SOMEONE OUT IF IT'S ALL LIMP?
IT'S NOT ABOUT
STRENGTH OR POWER.
YOU GOT TO BE FLUID.
HUH?
YOU HAVE TO BE LIKE WATER.
HMM.
YOU SEE WHAT I'M SAYING.
NOT EVEN A LITTLE BIT.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
COME AT ME WITH A KNIFE.
HEH. YOU'RE GONNA GET HURT.
JUST DO IT.
HERE I COME!
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
YOU'RE TENSE. I'M CALM.
YOU APPLY EXCESSIVE FORCE.
I CONTROL THAT FORCE
THROUGH FLUID MOTION.
THAT MEANS RELAXING
THE WHOLE BODY
SO IT CAN REACT INSTANTLY
WITHOUT RESISTANCE,
YOU KNOW, WITHOUT THOUGHT.
DO YOU SEE NOW?
IT MEANS BECOMING
LIKE CLEAR WATER.
WATER.
RIGHT.
WATER CAN TAKE ANY FORM.
IT DRIFTS WITHOUT
EFFORT ONE MOMENT,
THEN POUNDS DOWN IN
A TORRENT THE VERY NEXT.
MAYBE I GET IT,
BUT THEN AGAIN, MAYBE NOT.
YOU YOUNG FOOL!
YOU SHOULD HAVE A LITTLE
RESPECT FOR YOUR ELDERS!
--HANG ON TO THIS.
--HUH?
MEET ME TONIGHT--
NO, TOMORROW NIGHT AT THE
CATHEDRAL ON THE EDGE OF TOWN.
WHAT? HEY, WAIT!
THERE HE IS! GET HIM!
HMM.
CASINOS AGAIN?
THE ONES AROUND HERE ARE
FAMOUS FOR STACKING THE DECK.
DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S HER MONEY.
ON TOP OF IT,
SHE TAKES OFF LIKE A BULLET,
AND WE NEVER KNOW
WHEN SHE'LL BE BACK.
WELL, NO USE WASTING TIME, HUH?
HOW ABOUT TAKING
IN SOME POCKET MONEY?
HMM?
PICCARO CALVINO
USUALLY A NICKEL-AND-DIME GUY.
BY SOME MIRACLE,
HE PULLED OFF
A BIG HIT THIS TIME.
PRICE IS DOUBLE IF WE
BRING IN THE WHOLE CREW.
HUH?
THIS IS WHAT THEY STOLE.
THEY'RE VERY RARE.
THESE PLANTS ARE USED
TO MAKE THE MEDS THAT
CURE VENUS SICKNESS.
THEY'RE VERY HARD TO GROW,
WORTH TENS OF MILLIONS EACH.
HUH?
SORRY!
WHERE'D HE GO?
KID CAN RUN. LET'S GO.
HEE HEE. NOT BAD. YEAH.
HUH?
[MEOW]
SHH.
I SAY WE KEEP IT,
DEFINITELY.
IT'S WORTH A LOT MORE
THAN THOSE HOODS.
THEIR REWARDS ARE CHUMP CHANGE.
NO. WE CAN'T.
HA! YOU HAD TO
THINK ABOUT THAT.
DON'T BE A DITZ.
THIS THING IS HOT.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS
TO HOLD ON TO.
SOMETIMES YOU'VE
GOT TO TAKE A RISK.
HOW MUCH YOU LOSE
AT THAT CASINO?
WHAT'S THAT?
PICCARO IS UP TO YOU.
I'LL GET ROCO.
UH, YOU'VE GOT
AN APPOINTMENT WITH HIM.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST WAIT?
THEY SAY THAT LADY BOUNTY
IS VERY FICKLE, YOU KNOW?
IT'S LADY LUCK, F.Y.I.
A WRECK SHOP.
--WHY WOULD THAT BE OUT THERE?
--DON'T KNOW.
THERE MIGHT BE
A FEW CRAZIES LIVING IN
THAT GODFORSAKEN
DESERT, BUT STILL...
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
BOTH HANDS UP!
I'M NOT A CRIMINAL.
WHOA. THAT MAKES ME SOUND MORE
LIKE A CRIMINAL, DOESN'T IT?
WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
SPIT IT OUT!
[GASP]
LET GO.
I'M SORRY.
I JUST CAME HERE TO SEE ROCO.
[GASP]
YOU MEAN YOU'RE A FRIEND OF HIS?
UH, WELL, NOT...
I'M GLAD.
[ZIP]
AHH.
[GRUNT]
HUH?
MAKE SURE YOU WASH
BOTH HANDS, SPORT.
BOSS, WE CAN'T
FIND HIM ANYWHERE.
UH, HI.
YOU KNOW, IT'S ALL BECAUSE
OF THOSE FLOATING PLANTS.
THEY'RE ONLY HERE ON VENUS.
SOMETIMES THEY
SEND DOWN SPORES
THAT LOOK JUST
LIKE FALLING SNOW.
MOST PEOPLE AREN'T AFFECTED
BY IT, BUT SOME OF US ARE.
I LOST SIGHT
COMPLETELY IN BOTH EYES.
MUST BE VERY HARD FOR YOU.
MMM, IT'S SURPRISING
HOW YOU ADAPT,
AND ALSO, IN A WAY,
YOU UNDERSTAND MORE
WHEN YOU CAN'T SEE.
WILL YOU GET BETTER?
IF WE SPEND A LOT OF MONEY.
TRUTH IS, I DON'T REALLY MIND
IF I HAVE TO STAY LIKE THIS,
BUT ROCO...
HE CARES ABOUT
HIS LITTLE SISTER.
LOOK. ROCO SENT ME
THIS YESTERDAY.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I KNOW EVERYONE SAYS
BAD THINGS ABOUT HIM,
AND I KNOW HE HANGS OUT
WITH SOME BAD PEOPLE, TOO,
BUT ROCO HAS A GOOD HEART.
YOU KNOW, I COULD BE
ONE OF THOSE BAD PEOPLE
HE HANGS AROUND WITH.
MAYBE.
GUESS YOU COULD BE ONE,
BUT IF YOU ARE,
YOU'RE VERY DIFFERENT.
I CAN FEEL THESE THINGS.
BOTH YOU AND ROCO HAVE
SOMETHING BEAUTIFUL INSIDE YOU.
IT'S HARD FOR MOST PEOPLE
TO SEE IT, BUT IT'S THERE.
I KNOW IT IS.
THAT'S WHY I'M SHARING
MY TEA WITH YOU.
SOMETHING BEAUTIFUL, HUH?
I'M AFRAID THAT... AFRAID THAT
I LOST THAT A LONG TIME AGO.
[LAUGHTER]
[DOOR OPENS]
[WHISTLE]
HEY, BABY!
WHOA!
I GOT AN EMPTY
CHAIR OVER HERE, HUH?
HUH? OK!
I WANT PICCARO!
TELL ME WHERE HE IS.
PICCARO?
WELL, I NEVER HEARD
OF THE GUY, SWEETHEART.
[LAUGHTER]
[GUNFIRE]
NOW HAVE YOU HEARD OF HIM?
WELL, AS A MATTER OF FACT...
HUH?
WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION?
THE PRICE OF SEEDS
FOR GREY ASH PLANTS?
I'M JUST ASKING.
WELL, JUST DON'T.
THOSE THINGS ARE LIKE GEMS.
YOU'RE LUCKY
IF YOU EVER SEE ONE.
OH, REALLY?
WELL, IT'D PROBABLY
BE HARD TO FIND A BUYER,
BUT IF YOU DID,
I'D SAY ABOUT 8 MILLION EACH.
WHY? DID YOU GET SOME?
NO.
I THOUGHT SO.
FIND PICCARO YET?
WE'LL HAVE HIM SOON.
JUST DON'T SCREW UP YOUR END.
NICE.
SO, IF IT ISN'T ROCO.
YOU CAN BE A NICE BOY
AND TELL US WHERE THE PLANT IS,
BUT IF YOU DON'T
WANT TO TELL US...
I'M REAL SORRY,
BUT I DROPPED IT.
GUESS YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BUY THAT, HUH?
SLICK.
HMM, MY LITTLE ROCO.
YOU KNOW, I HEARD YOU HAVE
A YOUNGER SISTER SOMEWHERE.
IS THAT TRUE?
SHE'S GOT NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS!
[CHUCKLES]
AND SHE WON'T IF YOU TELL US
WHERE YOU PUT THE PLANT.
UH, IT'S, UH--
AAH!
HUH?
I WANT TO KNOW WHERE PICCARO IS.
A QUICK ANSWER WOULD BE GOOD.
OK. Y' 'ON'T HA'
TO 'E 'O 'OUGH.
WHAT? WHAT'D YOU SAY?
I CAN' 'REATHE!
[FOOTSTEPS]
YO.
OH, UH, SO YOU FOUND
THE OLD PLACE, HUH?
AND I BROUGHT IT LIKE YOU SAID.
SORRY, BUT I TOOK A PEEK INSIDE.
I SEE. SO YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
GREY ASH.
HUMBLE NAME
FOR SUCH AN AMAZING PLANT.
IT'S WORTH
10 TIMES THE BOUNTY
ON YOU AND ALL OF
YOUR BUDDIES COMBINED.
[GASP]
DON'T MOVE.
SO YOU'RE
A BOUNTY HUNTER, HUH?
YOU'RE HERE TO NAB ME
AND TAKE ME IN, AREN'T YOU?
STELLA NEEDS THIS.
THAT'S THE WHOLE POINT,
ISN'T IT?
HUH?
GET OUT OF HERE QUICK,
OR THEY'RE GONNA KILL YOU!
I GOT SET UP! IT WAS
A STUPID WILD GOOSE CHASE!
JET, ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
WHAT?
WAIT A MINUTE. PLEASE!
HE BROUGHT THE PLANT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANTED.
NOW LET HIM GO, PLEASE.
I'M ASKING YOU.
YOUR PATSY MADE
A GOOD DELIVERY BOY, ROCO.
HERE'S MY THANKS.
HUH?
YOU, GET HIM!
TAKE HIM OUT AND DO IT QUICK!
PICCARO CALVINO,
HOLD IT RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE.
SHE COULD BE A LITTLE MORE
DELICATE ABOUT THIS.
WHOA. EASY, FAYE!
THERE'S NO REWARD
IF THEY'RE ALL DEAD, REMEMBER?
DAMN! THESE GUYS
ARE BOUNTY HUNTERS!
GET THAT THING BACK NOW!
ROCO!
OH!
HA HA HA!
[GUNSHOT]
ROCO!
[GRUNTS]
THOSE STUPID IDIOTS.
PUT YOUR HANDS UP.
YOU'VE ALREADY
CAUSED ME ENOUGH TROUBLE.
COME ON. HANG IN THERE.
YOU HEAR ME?
ROCO!
MASTER, YOU SEE IT?
I WAS FLUID LIKE WATER.
YEAH. DON'T TRY
TO TALK ANYMORE.
WE'LL HAVE A DOCTOR HERE
IN A COUPLE OF MINUTES,
SO HEY!
I HAVE A FAVOR.
IN THE MUSIC BOX AT STELLA'S...
LEAVE IT TO ME. STELLA'S
GONNA BE ALL RIGHT, ROCO.
THANKS.
OK. HANG ON.
NOW, DON'T DIE. DON'T DIE!
[GRUNTS]
I WONDER, IF I HAD MET
YOU EARLIER IN MY LIFETIME,
DO YOU THINK THAT
WE WOULD HAVE BEEN FRIENDS?
DR. PENSKE, ALL 199.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
COME IN.
ROCO, IS THAT YOU?
IT'S ME INSTEAD.
OH. HEY, YOU KNOW
WHAT ROCO DID, HUH?
HE GOT ME SOME GREY ASH
FROM THE SEEDLINGS
AND MONEY FOR TREATMENT.
THE DOCTOR SAYS MY EYES
WILL BE ALL BETTER NOW.
ISN'T IT GREAT?
I WANT THE FIRST THING
I SEE TO BE ROCO.
SO TELL HIM TO COME
AND VISIT ME RIGHT NOW.
TELL HIM I CAN'T WAIT.
OH, SPIKE, IS HE IN JAIL?
NO.
THEN WHY HASN'T
HE COME TO SEE ME?
HE'S DEAD, ISN'T HE?
I SEE.
STELLA.
IT'S OK. YOU CAN LEAVE NOW.
HE MUST HAVE DIED
BECAUSE HE WAS DOING SOMETHING
THAT WAS WRONG, I'M SURE.
IT'S BETTER
IF YOU LEAVE FOR TODAY.
IT'S JUST THAT...
I NEVER GOT TO SEE ROCO
ONCE WITH MY OWN EYES.
HEY, WHAT WAS HE REALLY LIKE?
YOU KNOW BETTER THAN
ANYONE WITHOUT LOOKING.
HE WAS A TERRIFIC GUY,
EXACTLY THE PERSON
YOU THOUGHT HE WAS.
[MUSIC BOX PLAYING]
STARTING NEXT WEEK,
ED WILL BE ON THE SCENE!
HA HA HA!
WHO ARE YOU?
UH, WELL,
ED WILL INTRODUCE ED.
FULL NAME EDWARD WONG
HAU PEPELU TIVRUSKY IV.
THAT'S A LONG NAME.
WHO THE HELL IS THIS?
ED MADE UP THAT NAME FOR ED.
ISN'T IT COOL?
IF YOU MADE IT UP,
HOW CAN YOU BE THE FOURTH?
NEXT EPISODE,
JAMMING WITH EDWARD.
DOES ANYONE
KNOW WHO THIS KID IS?
WATCH IT.