♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
TO BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1.
LET'S JAM. ♪
IT'S REALLY NOT
MY STYLE, YOU KNOW.
JUST SITTING AROUND
WAITING FOR NOTHING LIKE THIS.
YOU PICK A POINT
AND YOU KEEP ON WAITING.
THAT'S THE SECRET TO
FISHING IN THE BIG POND.
MAYBE YOU PICKED
THE WRONG POINT.
OR MAYBE IT'S
THE WRONG POND.
OR MAYBE THE BAIT
SHOULD STOP COMPLAINING.
WHAT ARE YOU FISHING FOR?
JUST YOUR
EVERYDAY PIRATES.
STARSHIP PIRATES,
THEY'RE CALLED.
PIRATES?
BARBARIC SLIME
WHO RANSACK SHIPS
AND TAKE WHATEVER THEY WANT.
LET'S KEEL HAUL
THE DIRTY SCALAWAGS!
WHAT THE HELL'S THE STORY
WITH SPIKE NOT BEING AROUND?
HE WENT TO HAVE
THE SHIP OVERHAULED,
AND HE NEVER CHECKED IN.
[YIPS]
THANKS THERE, LITTLE BUDDY.
MAN, THAT SPIKE DID IT AGAIN.
WHAT'S HE DOING WITHOUT
CHECKING IN WITH US LIKE THAT?
YOU'RE LATE, DOOHAN.
--YES!
--HUH?
YES! YES, YES, YES!
--HEY.
--HMM?
HEY!
STRIKE 3. BATTER OUT,
AND THE GAME'S OVER.
OH, MAN!
[GROWLS]
DAMN IT! WHY THE HELL DIDN'T
THEY SEND IN A PINCH HITTER?
ATEWOOD'S TOO OLD!
DON'T THEY KNOW THAT BY NOW?
DON'T YOU THINK SO?
WHERE THE HELL'S DOOHAN?
I'M AFRAID HE'S A BUSY,
OLD MAN AT THE MOMENT.
I'M MILES, HIS ASSISTANT.
GOOD TO MEET YOU.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[SPITS]
MAN, HE WAS THE TOUGHEST
ROOKIE AROUND
WHEN HE STARTED 14 YEARS AGO.
HE SLAMMED THE BALLS
ONE AFTER THE OTHER
AND BROUGHT THE BLUE SOX BACK
FROM THE BASEMENT THAT SEASON.
BUT TODAY, RANDY HILL HIT
3 CONSECUTIVE HOME RUNS.
HOW DO YOU COMPETE
WITH THAT?
OH, MAN! YOU SHOULD
HAVE HEARD THE CROWD!
THEY WENT CRAZY!
HEY, UH, DO PEOPLE EVER TELL YOU
THAT YOU DON'T TALK MUCH?
HEY, BRO, DO PEOPLE EVER TELL
YOU THAT YOU TALK TOO MUCH?
HMM, I GUESS SO.
THAT'S SWORDFISH
THERE, ISN'T IT?
THAT SHIP IN THE BACK.
--YEAH.
--WHOA!
ISN'T THAT THE AMAZING MONORACER
THAT THE OLD MAN BUILT?
SHE'S JUST AN OLD SHIP TO ME.
CAN'T GET RID OF HER.
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL, MAN.
I CAN'T BEGIN TO TELL
YOU HOW MANY TIMES
I TRIED TO QUIT BEING
A BLUE SOX FAN OVER THE YEARS.
I TELL YOU, IT'S LIKE
I'M FALLING IN LOVE
WITH THE WRONG WOMAN
OVER AND OVER!
[EXPLOSION]
AW, GEEZ! NOT AGAIN!
HEY! OLD MAN!
[FOOTSTEPS]
HEY. LONG TIME, NO SEE
HEY. MILES,
WHERE'S THE CHECKLIST?
IT'S THERE.
I PUT IT ON THE PILOT SEAT.
HE'S TRYING TO FIX UP...
THAT OLD ANCIENT RELIC?
I THINK IT'S USELESS.
THE COMPUTER ISN'T COMPATIBLE
WITH THE OLD
MONOSYSTEM IT'S GOT.
MILES! I'LL NEED
AN E.V. TRANSMITTER,
A MAIN GEAR ABSORBER, REBUILT,
AND A 3-8
PNEUMATIC TUBE, PRONTO.
A 3-8? WE DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING RARE LIKE THAT.
THEN ORDER IT FROM REGGIE.
HE'S GOT TO HAVE IT.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
HE SURE KNOWS HOW TO USE PEOPLE.
SEE YOU LATER.
WHAT A HOBBY.
[ALARM]
--YOU CATCH IT, FAYE?
--NO, NOT ME. I-- WHERE?
IT'S CLOSE! DAMN!
IT'S THAT ROTTEN BAIT.
WATCH IT.
HEY, IT'S
A GOOD-LOOKING MACHINE.
TRANSFERRING WEALTH FROM
THE FORTUNATELY UNFORTUNATE
CAN BE VERY FULFILLING.
IT'S WHAT CHARITY IS ALL ABOUT.
DON'T YOU THINK SO?
HA! YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
SOCIAL REFORM ALL THE WAY.
EXACTLY.
POOR UNFORTUNATES LIKE US
HAVE EVERY RIGHT TO TAKE IT.
--WHAT IS THIS?
--WHAT IS IT? THE COPS?
OK. THAT'S ENOUGH, BOYS.
BOUNTY HUNTER
HOUSE CALL. HARMAN?
THATTA GIRL. COME ON IN.
HEY! LOOK OUT, FAYE!
AAH! UGH!
WHAT THE HELL?
[GROWLS]
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
HA HA HA!
HEY, RUTH. THERE'S
ONE RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
--IT'S A BIG ONE.
--I SEE IT.
MAN! WHAT A PIECE OF CRAP!
PAYBACK TIME, PAL.
[BEEPING]
[TYPING]
NOW.
MONOSYSTEM MALFUNCTION.
EMERGENCY PILOT PROGRAM...
OH!
STOP IT!
DO YOU HEAR ME?
DAMN IT!
[GURGLING]
[WHIRRING]
THE MONOSYSTEM SOUNDS
SHAKEN UP PRETTY BADLY.
SHUT IT DOWN!
THE ACCELERATOR PUMP
IS COMPLETELY SHOT.
I KNOW THAT.
AND ANOTHER THING I NOTICED
THERE'S NO SILENCER
ON THE FUEL INJECTOR.
--THERE'S NO NEED.
--WHAT?
BUT IT'S TOO NOISY
AND THE VIBRATIONS.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
A SILENCER WOULD ONLY MASK
THE UNDERLYING PROBLEMS.
HUH?
NOW HURRY UP
AND CONNECT THE INJECTOR.
YOU KNOW, NOWADAYS,
A 3-8 PNEUMATIC TUBE
ISN'T IN STYLE ANYMORE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GO WITH
A 5-0 AND UPDATE THIS RELIC?
ENOUGH, MILES!
WE CAN EVEN KICK IT
INTO FREESTYLE WITH
FULL AUTO NAVIGATION!
OH!
NOW, LISTEN UP.
YOU EITHER WORK FOR THIS
MACHINE OR IT WORKS FOR YOU.
MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO--
JUST GO.
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED, HUH?
YOU'RE GOING TO CHASE OFF
ANOTHER ASSISTANT
IF YOU KEEP THAT UP.
OOH!
WELL, MAYBE I'M JUST LIKE OLD
SWORDFISH THERE, SPIKE, MY BOY.
I'M JUST TRYING TO MAKE A POINT.
HAVEN'T EVER HEARD
THAT ONE BEFORE.
IF YOU KEEP ON
PUSHING IT LIKE THIS,
YOU'RE REALLY GOING TO GET
CUT DOWN TO SIZE FOR GOOD.
SORRY. I'M NOT EXACTLY
THE DELICATE, CAUTIOUS TYPE.
[SIPPING]
IT'S HERE. I GOT THAT RARE 3-8
PNEUMATIC TUBE YOU REQUESTED.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
HELLO.
OH, IT'S YOU.
THE MYSTERIOUS MISSING GUY.
WHERE YOU BEEN HIDING OUT?
I'M STILL AT DOOHAN'S SHOP.
SO WHERE'S JET?
HE'S GOT HIS HANDS
FULL RIGHT NOW.
HE SAID HE WAS WORKING ON SOME
KIND OF BACTERIA OR SOMETHING.
BACTERIA?
NO, IT'S A VIRUS, FAYE.
A COMPUTER VIRUS.
WELL, IT'S THE SAME THING.
UM... UHUH.
STARTING WITH THE MONOSYSTEM,
ORBIT CALCULATOR,
NAVIGATOR, ENGINE CONTROL,
COMMUNICATION CIRCUIT
THEY'RE ALL GONE.
I DON'T GET IT.
HOW ABOUT USING ENGLISH, HUH?
THE COMPUTER'S KAPUT,
AND WE'RE DRIFTING THROUGH SPACE
TOWARD CERTAIN OBLIVION.
UGH.
DEFINITELY GOT THAT.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT'S THE NEWEST ONE.
CAN'T FIND IT ELSEWHERE,
I CAN PROMISE YOU THAT.
THE MONOCOMPUTER.
HOW ABOUT 150?
NO. 100,000.
IT'S A BARGAIN.
A BARGAIN, HUH?
WELL, NOT WHEN THE SCRAPS
CAN BE TRACED BACK.
SO, HOW'S THE DEALER?
WHERE DID YOU
GET IT FROM, HUH?
YOU SAY A TRUCK?
WHAT KIND OF A TRUCK?
A PENGUIN.
DELIVERY TRUCK.
--A DELIVERY TRUCK?
--HUH?
ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THE INFORMATION?
YEAH. THEY WERE DOING BUSINESS
BY THE ORBIT DRIVE-IN.
I GET IT.
IT WOULDN'T BE SUSPICIOUS
IF ANYONE SAW
A DELIVERY TRUCK
DRIVING AROUND THERE.
SO THEN, HOW ARE WE
GOING TO COUNTER THE HACKS?
DON'T GET YOURSELF HARPOONED.
AND? ANYTHING ELSE?
THEY DARED TO CALL THIS SHIP
A WORTHLESS PIECE OF CRAP,
AND THEY MADE A COMPLETE
MESS OF MY HAMMERHEAD.
UNLIKE SOMEONE ELSE HERE,
I ALWAYS RETURN WHAT I OWE.
GEE, WHAT
AN ADMIRABLE VIRTUE.
I'M REALLY NOT UP FOR THIS.
I JUST GOT AN INVOICE FROM
DOOHAN WITH YOUR NAME ON IT.
[EXHALES]
IF THEY'RE PHYSICALLY SENDING
THE COMPUTER VIRUS TO US,
THEN THEY HAVEN'T DEVELOPED
AN ANTIVIRUS PROGRAM FOR IT.
HERE'S THE PLAN.
WE'LL SURPRISE THEM WITH
OUR OWN SECRET WEAPON.
WHAT, JET? THAT'S JUST
A NORMAL TRANSMITTER.
IF WE GET INFECTED
BY THE VIRUS,
CUT OFF THE ENTIRE MONOSYSTEM.
NAVIGATION AND
COMMUNICATIONS WILL CRASH.
EXACTLY. THAT'S WHY
I'M GOING TO ASSIST YOU
THROUGH THIS FROM HERE ON.
THIS USES THE OLD SATELLITE
TRANSMISSION WAVE
SIGNALS FOR GUIDANCE,
SO IT IN EFFECT BYPASSES
THE MONOSYSTEM.
AND ANOTHER RUN SCORES
AGAINST THE BLUE SOX.
HENDERSON LOOKS
IN FOR THE SIGN...
THAT'S SOME SECRET WEAPON
YOU GOT THERE, JET.
HENDERSON THROWS,
HIGH AND AWAY. BALL 2.
BOSH IS 02 IN TODAY'S GAME.
HE HASN'T BEEN PLAYING...
[BOTH GASP]
[GROWLS]
HERE'S THE PITCH.
SWING, AND IT'S A LONG DRIVE!
OH! JUST FOUL!
IT WAS A PENGUIN
YOU SAID, WASN'T IT?
YEAH. I'M SURE IT WAS
A PURPLE PENGUIN.
NO ONE SAID TWO OF THEM.
WAIT A MINUTE. IT MIGHT BE
A REAL DELIVERY SERVICE.
WE'VE GOT TO FIGURE OUT
IF THEY'RE LEGIT OR NOT.
THAT'S EASY.
WE JUST SHOOT AND SEE WHO
HIGHTAILS IT OUT OF THERE.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I AGREE WITH YOU ON SOMETHING.
HUH? WAIT A MINUTE!
DID YOU CONSIDER THE POSSIBILITY
THEY'RE BOTH REAL?
UH, THEY'RE BOTH RUNNING.
I GUESS WE DIDN'T
DISCUSS THAT OPTION.
YOU HANDLE THAT ONE.
PAYBACK TIME
FOR YESTERDAY, BOYS.
AAH! FORGIVE US! PLEASE!
WE'LL PAY THE PACKING
TICKET! I PROMISE!
I GOTCHA!
SPIKE! KEEP THEM OUT!
IT'LL BE A MESS IF THEY
SPREAD THE VIRUS INSIDE.
I KNOW.
...FROM BEHIND.
2 OUTS.
KOLINSKY'S UP NEXT.
LET'S SEE WHAT
YOU GOT, HOTSHOT.
--HE'S HERE.
--METAL MALLET HEAD.
I THINK HE'S GOING
AFTER THE ARM.
THE LITTLE WISE ASS.
YOU THERE, RUTH?
READY TO GO ANY TIME.
[CACKLES]
GERONIMO!
AAH!
HAVE A TASTE OF THIS.
EXCELLENT!
BINGO!
A PERSISTENT,
LITTLE DEVIL.
AAH!
[CACKLES]
CUT THE MONOSYSTEM!
I DID!
LOOK LIKE THE IDIOT CUT OFF
HIS MONOSYSTEM, HARMAN.
HEY, GEORGE.
LOOK AT THIS.
AND HE'S IN THE EARTH'S
GRAVITATIONAL FIELD! HA HA!
HUH?
OLD MAN! LISTEN HERE!
THIS SOUNDS PRETTY BAD!
YOU DID IT BEFORE, RIGHT?
LIKE I REMEMBER.
NO USE! THERE'S
NOTHING WE CAN DO!
YOU IDIOT! HURRY UP AND DO
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS QUICK!
GODDAMN IT! MOVE IT!
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
WE'RE FALLING!
FALLING!
SPIKE! I'LL BE RIGHT THERE!
I'M CALCULATING THE
INTERCEPTION COURSE YOU'RE ON.
UNTIL THAT TIME, SOMEHOW
KEEP CONTROL MANUALLY.
EVEN IF EVERYTHING WAS NORMAL,
IT'S TOUGH TO GET OUT
OF THIS DAMN PLACE.
LIKE I NEED YOU
TO TELL ME THAT.
UGH. AND I JUST
OVERHAULED THIS THING.
[CRASH]
HELL... I'LL TAKE MY CHANCES.
[WHISTLES]
--SPIKE! ABOVE YOU!
--WHAT?
THAT OLD HULL LOOKS
LIKE A GODDESS TO ME.
DAMN! THE VIRUS!
--YOU OK?
--I'M STILL ALIVE.
LET'S REGROUP.
NO WAY! YOU'RE KIDDING,
RIGHT, OLD MAN?
I MEAN, YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS ABOUT
THIS ANTIQUE PIECE OF JUNK!
I WOULDN'T DO ANYTHING
I WASN'T SERIOUS ABOUT.
[LAUGHS]
DON'T JUST STAND THERE!
GET A MOVE ON!
AND GO GET ME SOME FUEL!
YES, SIR!
SPIKE!
CAN YOU HEAR ME, BUD?
I'VE GOT A CALCULATION.
IT'LL TAKE 7 HOURS FOR ME
TO RENDEZVOUS WITH YOU.
COME ON, JET.
YOU'RE JOKING, RIGHT?
WE'RE TOO CLOSE TO EARTH.
THE ORBITAL PATHS
I CAN TAKE ARE LIMITED.
UH, ISN'T THERE A WAY
YOU CAN JUST SWING ON BY?
IF I CONTINUE PLUNGING
IN AT THIS ANGLE,
BOTH THE BEBOP AND THE SWORDFISH
WILL BURN TO NOTHING.
UGH!
HEY, JET.
HMM?
YOU KNOW, I, UH...
GOT SOME WHISKEY
HIDDEN BEHIND THE FRIDGE.
WHY DON'T YOU
HELP YOURSELF, BUD?
HUH? WHAT WENT WRONG?
THE FUEL TANKS ARE EMPTY.
THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO NOW.
HOW ABOUT I
RENDEZVOUS AND TOW YOU BACK,
IN EXCHANGE FOR THE WHISKEY?
I HEARD THE CONVERSATION.
GIVE ME THE EXACT COORDINATES
OF THE SWORDFISH.
DOOHAN!
HOW THE HELL DID YOU?
SPIKE, FIND SOMETHING THAT
CAN BE USED AS AN AIR BRAKE,
SO YOU CAN DECELERATE.
DECELERATE?
IF YOU DECELERATE WITHIN
THE EARTH'S ATMOSPHERE,
THE GRAVITATIONAL PULL
WILL ACCELERATE YOU INSTEAD,
WHICH WILL GIVE YOU
ENOUGH SPEED TO ESCAPE.
HOWEVER, YOU HAVE TO MAINTAIN
THE SHIP AT A CERTAIN ANGLE.
TOO FAR IN EITHER DIRECTION
AND YOU'LL BE THROWN OUT TO
THE OTHER END OF THE UNIVERSE.
LIKE I SAID BEFORE, I'M NOT
THE DELICATE, CAUTIOUS TYPE.
SPIKE.
HMM?
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT, BOY.
I DIDN'T GIVE YOU THE SWORDFISH
FOR NOTHING, YOU KNOW.
YEAH. DON'T YOU GO
AND CRASH EITHER, OLD MAN.
MAXIMUM PROPULSION!
THERE'S STILL TIME TO CHANGE
YOUR MIND AND LEAVE, MILES.
NEGATIVE. BLUE SOX FANS
NEVER LEAVE THE GAME EARLY.
[CHUCKLES]
--LET'S GO!
--ALL RIGHT!
I'M FLYING!
AND I THOUGHT
I WAS AFRAID TO FLY!
LOWER THE NOSE 0.6 DEGREES.
YOU'RE IN TOO DEEP, SPIKE!
YOU'LL BURN TO A CRISP!
HUH?
THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE.
IT'S IN THERE.
IT WENT IN.
THAT WAS PERFECT!
DOOHAN, YOU SAVED MY ASS.
NOT YET.
HUH?
MOST OF THE HEAT RESISTANT
TILES HAVE PEELED OFF.
THE TEMPERATURE'S RISING.
THE LANDING WHEELS
AREN'T RETRACTING!
YEP, AND THE NUMBER 2
NOZZLE WON'T WORK EITHER.
WHAT?!
ARE YOU FOR REAL?
WE CAN'T LAND WITHOUT THEM.
OH, WELL.
WHATEVER HAPPENS... HAPPENS.
[MILES SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
SOMEBODY HELP!
[CACKLING]
NEXT EPISODE.
PIERROT LA FOU.