[CHURCH BELL RINGING]
♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
TO BLOW THIS SCENE ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1,
LET'S JAM ♪
HEY, SPIKE.
[CLICK]
HUH?
IT'S READY.
I'M JUST ABOUT FINISHED.
WHAT'S COOKING?
SPECIAL.
BELL PEPPERS AND BEEF.
ASIMOV SOLENSAN.
HE'S OUR NEXT TARGET.
UH, LISTEN, JET.
THIS GUY'S A MAJOR PLAYER
IN THE SYNDICATE.
OPERATES ALL AROUND
THE ASTEROIDS.
YOU SAID
BELL PEPPERS AND BEEF.
HIS NAME'S ASIMOV SOLENSAN.
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
THERE'S NO BEEF IN HERE.
SO YOU WOULDN'T REALLY CALL IT
BELL PEPPERS AND BEEF,
NOW, WOULD YOU?
YES. I WOULD.
WELL, IT'S NOT!
IT IS WHEN YOU'RE BROKE,
ALL RIGHT?
WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE MILLION WOOLONG REWARD
WE GOT FOR THAT LAST GUY?
THE REPAIR BILL
FOR THAT CRUISER YOU WRECKED,
AND THE ONE FROM
THAT SHOP YOU TRASHED,
AND THE MEDICAL BILL
FROM THE COP YOU INJURED
KILL THE DOUGH!
NOW, 3 DAYS AGO,
THERE WAS A BIG SHOOTOUT
BETWEEN HIS GROUP
AND A RIVAL SYNDICATE.
HE KILLED HIS OWN GUYS,
THEN TOOK OFF LIKE THE WIND.
WORD IS HE'S HIDING OUT WITH
SOME SWEET THING IN TIJUANA.
T.J. THAT PLACE
IS FOR SMALL FRIES.
YEAH, WELL, THIS SMALL
FRY'S WORTH 2 1/2 MILLION.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE IT.
SPEAKING OF BEEF,
THEY SAY IN T.J.
THE GARNITAS ARE
OUT OF THIS WORLD.
ATTENTION, PLEASE.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[WHISTLING A TUNE]
I'LL HEAD OVER THERE
AFTER I HIT UP
THE COPS FOR SOME CLUES.
ALL RIGHT.
AND I'LL CHECK IN
WITH OLD MAN BULL.
YOU THINK YOU CAN TRUST
THAT OLD CODGER?
[WHISTLING A TUNE]
NICE TURN. REAL EASY.
[BEEPING]
THEIF!
THIS AGAIN?
SON OF A BITCH.
TAKING MY MONEY LIKE THAT,
YOU CHEATING DOGS.
WHY, THE ONLY REASON
YOU CAN EVEN LIVE HERE
IS 'CAUSE OF WHAT I DONE.
I BUSTED MY TAIL
TO DIG THAT GATE.
FOR CRIMINY'S SAKES,
YOU ALWAYS SAY THE SAME
THING WHEN YOU'RE LOSING.
WE ALL DUG THAT GATE
TOGETHER, AND YOU KNOW IT.
THAT WE DID. WE WORKED
LIKE THERE WAS NO TOMORROW.
AND WHAT DO WE GOT
TO SHOW FOR IT?
[DOOR OPENS]
HUH?
GIMME A BEER.
AND I WILL HAVE A BLOODY MARY.
IN FACT, MAKE IT A DOUBLE.
I'VE GOT THE VODKA,
BUT I'M AFRAID I'M FRESH
OUT OF TOMATO JUICE.
I'M SURE THERE'S ONE CAN
IN THE BACK ROOM.
I'LL CHECK.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[INSECT BUZZING]
PREMIUM REDEYE. YOU'RE A
BUYER. YOU KNOW THE SCORE.
CHECK IT OUT.
IS THAT REAL BLOODY EYE?
HEH HEH HEH. UHH.
I'M GOING TO NEED
A LITTLE PROOF.
LET'S HAVE A DEMONSTRATION.
OHH!
YEAH, KEEP THOSE EYES OPEN.
[MEOW]
UHH!
UHHUHH!
[GRUNTING]
OHUHH!
[CRASH]
[WIND CHIMES TINKLING]
THIS IS REAL MYSTIC AND ALL,
BUT, UH, DO YOU HAVE
ANYTHING TO EAT HERE?
[STOMACH GROWLING]
I SEE.
THE REDEYED COYOTE
WILL APPEAR IN THE ZONA NORTE
AT THE FAR END OF TOWN.
THAT IS WHAT I SEE.
A REDEYED COYOTE
NORTH OF TOWN?
YOU, SWIMMING BIRD.
THE SWIMMING BIRD
WILL MEET A WOMAN.
THE BIRD WILL BE HUNTED
BY THIS WOMAN,
AND THEN DEATH.
ONE MORE TIME.
WHAT'S THAT?
I WAS KILLED
ONCE BEFORE BY A WOMAN.
YOU TAKE WOMEN
TOO LIGHTLY, MY FRIEND.
ON THE CONTRARY.
CATCH YOU LATER.
WAKANTANKA, GUIDE HIS SPIRIT.
[DOOR CLOSES]
PRESIDENTE, EH? THINK
I'LL HAVE SOME, ON THE HOUSE.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
HMM?
[FOOTSTEPS]
HUH? DAMN.
JUST LOOK AT THIS.
ASIMOV WENT BERSERK.
NO JOKE. WE GOT
TO TAKE CARE OF HIM
BEFORE THE COPS MOVE IN.
MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST
LET THE COPS DEAL WITH HIM.
AS LONG AS HE'S
USING THAT REDEYE ON HIMSELF,
YOU CAN'T BEAT HIM.
WE GOT TO. IF WE DON'T
GET THAT BLOODY EYE BACK,
TRUST ME, WE'LL ALL BE
TWISTIN' IN THE WIND.
MAYBE SO, HUH?
YO.
HUH? UHH!
TELL ME SOME MORE.
I AM STARVING.
[BEEPING]
HMM?
SO YOU'RE HUNGRY,
TOO, HUH, BABY?
[WHISTLING A TUNE]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[THUMP]
HUH?
[WATER RUNNING]
YOU KNOW, IT'S BETTER TO JUST
LEAVE THE WATER RUNNING...
SO YOU DON'T CLOG THE DRAIN.
[WHISTLING A TUNE]
--UHH.
--OOPS.
--SORRY.
UH, THANK YOU.
UH, EXCUSE ME?
HMM?
HMM. IT'S YOUR HOT DOG.
YEAH, I CAN SEE THAT.
JUST KEEP IT.
MMF. MMM.
[CHUCKLING]
[CHUCKLES]
HEH HEH. SORRY.
MY STOMACH JUST
TOOK OVER MY BRAIN.
IT DOES THAT SOMETIMES.
REALLY?
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
NICE SHIP.
YEAH, IT'S A BLAST
FROM THE PAST.
I'VE HAD IT FOR 10 YEARS.
IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S BEEN AROUND.
GUESS YOU COULD SAY
WE'VE DONE SOME TRAVELING.
I'M ACTUALLY
A TRAVELING PERFORMER.
[CHUCKLES]
I CAN'T TELL WHEN YOU'RE
JOKING AND WHEN YOU'RE NOT.
YEAH, I HEAR THAT A LOT.
EVER BEEN TO MARS?
I WAS BORN ON MARS.
I HEAR THEY HAVE
EVERYTHING THERE,
NOT LIKE HERE.
THERE'S PARKS AND FESTIVALS,
AND THE PEOPLE ARE HAPPY THERE.
IT MUST BE A GREAT
PLACE TO LIVE.
SURE, IF YOU'RE RICH.
THEN I'M SURE
WE WILL BE QUITE HAPPY.
PLANNING TO ESCAPE
TO MARS, HUH?
HUH? GO AHEAD AND RUN.
HOW FAR DO YOU
THINK YOU'LL GET?
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M JUST
AN OLDFASHIONED COWBOY.
YOU'RE A BOUNTY HUNTER.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
AND YOU ARE AFTER US.
YOUR BOYFRIEND IS SICK.
HE'S A SMALL FRY.
I DON'T BOTHER WITH HIS TYPE.
A WISE DECISION.
ACK! UGH! UHH!
NOW WHO'S THE SMALL FRY?
[CHOKING]
ASIMOV, THAT'S ENOUGH.
LET HIM GO.
ADIOS, COWBOY.
WHY DID YOU STOP ME?
HE WOULD'VE BEEN DEAD
IN ANOTHER MINUTE.
I WANTED TO SEE HIM DIE.
ASIMOV, PLEASE.
THIS HAS TO STOP.
I THINK YOU LIKED HIM...
DIDN'T YOU?
YOU LEFT ME THERE
FOR SO LONG, ASIMOV.
I WAS JUST WAITING
FOR YOU TO PICK ME UP.
LET'S GO, ASIMOV,
LIKE YOU PROMISED.
I WANT TO GET OUT OF THIS LIFE.
I KNOW THAT I CAN
BE HAPPY ON MARS.
HAVING OURSELVES
A LITTLE NAP, HUH?
I HAD A SWEET DREAM.
THAT'S HEARTWARMING.
AND YOU CAN GO RIGHT AHEAD
AND FINISH YOUR DREAM
BACK ON THE BEBOP.
I'M CASHING IN
MY CHIPS ON THIS ONE.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO CATCH THE GUY.
THERE'S NO WAY TO WIN IT.
WHEN ASIMOV
LEFT HIS SYNDICATE,
HE SNUCK SOME
STUFF OUT WITH HIM.
SERIOUS BREW. THIS STUFF'S
A TOTAL MINDFRAG.
IT'S A NEW KIND OF EYE SPRAY
THE SYNDICATE COOKED UP.
VERY PURE. TAKES 2 MONTHS
TO MAKE ONE VIAL.
OUR BOY TOOK OFF
WITH EVERY DROP,
WHICH MADE
HIM RATHER UNPOPULAR.
THEY KEEP SENDING
HIT TEAMS AFTER HIM,
BUT ALL THEY GET
BACK ARE CORPSES.
SEEMS ASIMOV'S BEEN PUMPING UP
BY DOING THE STUFF HIMSELF.
IT'S CALLED BLOODY EYE.
NO KIDDING.
YOU KNOW THEY'RE
PLANNING TO GO TO MARS?
MARS?
BUT BEFORE THAT,
THEY'VE GOT TO SELL THESE.
IS THAT WHAT I THINK IT IS?
YEAH. I GRABBED IT
OUT OF HIS POCKET.
YOU... MET HIM?
YEAH, SO TO SPEAK.
HEH HEH.
HE NAILED YOU, HUH?
THE REDEYED COYOTE
WILL APPEAR IN THE ZONA NORTE
AT THE FAR END OF TOWN.
[SIREN WAILING]
[EXHALES]
THIS AGAIN?
DAMN SON OF A BITCH.
TAKING MY MONEY LIKE THAT,
YOU CHEATIN' DOGS.
WHY, THE ONLY REASON
YOU COULD EVEN EAT HERE
IS 'CAUSE OF WHAT I DONE.
I BUSTED MY TAIL
TO PLANT THOSE CROPS
ALONG WITH MY 2 GOOD BUDDIES.
WE'RE THE BUDDIES
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YEAH, SURE. THAT WE ARE.
WE PLANTED THOSE SEEDS
LIKE THERE WAS NO TOMORROW.
YOU WERE ALWAYS
PLANTING SEEDS
OF A DIFFERENT
KIND, THOUGH.
HUH?
SO, DO YOU HAVE
ANY BLOODY MARYS?
I ONLY HAVE BEER.
I GOT TOMATO JUICE.
HOW MUCH?
30 MILLION WOOLONGS
FOR 50 PACKS.
15 MILLION WOOLONGS.
I'M IN A HURRY.
I'VE GOT OTHER CUSTOMERS.
SHOW ME.
OH LOOKING FOR THIS?
DO YOU KNOW
HOW MUCH YOU'RE WORTH?
WHAT?
2.5 MILLION WOOLONGS.
THAT'S YOUR BOUNTY.
I SAID YOU WERE A SMALL FRY.
YOU LOOK SURPRISED.
YOU LOOK RIDICULOUS
IN THAT OUTFIT.
I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T
AFTER MY BOUNTY.
THERE'S NO THRILL IN THE
CHEAP ONES, ASIMOV, YOU KNOW?
I THINK YOU DO BETTER
AS A THIEF, BOUNTY BOY.
NOW, HAND IT OVER.
SURE. I'D BE GLAD TO.
I HAVE TO PAY YOU BACK,
DON'T I?
OOH! HA HA HA.
[GROWLING]
YOU TRUST YOUR EYES
TOO MUCH, ASIMOV.
HA. YOU'RE NOT
A CHAMELEON, YOU KNOW.
CAN'T SEE EVERYWHERE AT ONCE.
AHH!
LET'S GO!
OVER THERE!
[TIRES SCREECH]
FOLLOW HER! UHH!
DON'T MOVE.
I DON'T WANT TO HURT YOU.
OH!
[GROWLS]
IDIOT!
IF WE LOSE THESE THINGS,
WE'RE FRAGGED.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
[TIRES SCREECHING]
UHH!
[BOTH GROAN]
HOW YOU DOING, KID?
WHAT?
YOU'RE LATE, JET! HUH?
DAMN.
ASIMOV.
STOP IT, PLEASE!
THAT STUFF IS GOING TO KILL YOU!
[GRUNTING]
NO!
AAH!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
WE WILL NEVER
GET OUT OF HERE NOW.
I'LL NEVER SEE MARS.
[GUNSHOT]
ADIOS.
HEY, SPIKE. GET IT
WHILE IT'S HOT, BUDDY.
HUH?
IT'S READY.
WHAT IS IT?
SPECIAL.
BELL PEPPERS AND BEEF.
WELL, THE SHOW'S
FINALLY UNDERWAY.
WHAT'S ALL THIS?
NEXT EPISODE,
WE'RE TOTALLY CHANGING GEARS.
IT'S GOING TO BE
ANIME FOR ALL AGES.
WHAT'S THE STORY?
HOUSE PETS WREAK HAVOC
THROUGHOUT THE STARS. WHAT?
HEH. NO, THE GUY
WHO TALKS TO ANIMALS
WILL NOT MAKE
AN APPEARANCE,
BUT ANYONE WHO LOVES ANIMALS
SHOULD GATHER ROUND
AND WATCH THIS SHOW.
HEY, CAN WE SAY
STUFF LIKE THAT?
I'M TAKING NO
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THIS.
CAUTION: SMALL CHILDREN
SHOULD SIT FAR BACK FROM THE TV.
COME ON. HOW FAR BACK?
ABOUT 3/4 OF A MILE.
--THAT'S TOO FAR.
--OK, HALF A MILE.