♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1.
LET'S JAM. ♪
[DOOR OPENS, BELL RINGS]
HMM?
I LIKE THOSE SHADES, MAN.
I LIKE EVERYTHING YOU GOT.
LOOKING TO MAKE
SOME BIG BUCKS?
I THINK YOU'D FIT
RIGHT IN HERE.
HUH.
YEAH.
[WHIMPERS]
YOU KNOW THE FIRST RULE
OF COMBAT?
[COCKS GUN]
HUH?
SHOOT THEM
BEFORE THEY SHOOT YOU.
[WHIMPERS]
QUITE AN ELABORATE WAY
TO GET ACQUAINTED.
I HAD NO IDEA THE LEGENDARY
LADY LUCK WAS STILL ALIVE.
POKER ALICE,
QUEEN OF HEARTS
THEY TELL TALES ABOUT YOU ON
EVERY ASTEROID FROM HERE TO T.J.
IF ALICE WAS STILL ALIVE,
SHE'D BE OVER 200 YEARS OLD.
THAT'S TRUE.
CONSIDERING, YOU'RE
LOOKING PRETTY GOOD.
HOTTEST GRANNY
IN THE STAR SYSTEM.
POKER ALICE NEVER LOST A GAME,
AND SHE NEVER CHEATED.
SHE WAS JUST A BORN WINNER.
MAYBE, AND MAYBE THAT'S
JUST PART OF THE LEGEND.
HMPH!
I UNDERSTAND YOU'VE ACCRUED
QUITE A LARGE DEBT.
WOULD YOU RATHER DEAL
WITH THE GALACTIC POLICE
OR ME, MS. QUEEN OF HEARTS?
A PROPHECY?
SO CHARLIE SAYS.
ONLY HANDS CAN WASH HANDS.
IF YOU WANT TO RECEIVE,
YOU HAVE TO GIVE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I WISH I COULD REMEMBER
THE EXACT WORDS.
ANYWAY, I THINK CHARLIE'S
TELLING US TO JUST DO IT.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF IT?
SOMEHOW, I DON'T
THINK CHARLIE PARKER
WOULD BE QUOTING GOETHE.
COME ON. IT'S JUST
A DREAM I HAD.
LIGHTEN UP.
I HAVE A FEELING THAT DREAM
IS GOING TO SUCK UP
OUR LAST 5,000 WOOLONGS.
I'M REALLY SORRY
TO MENTION THIS...
--HMM?
--NO SMOKING IN HERE.
HMM?
[PIANO PLAYING]
YOU BETTER NOT PLAY HERE.
YOUR EYES ARE TOO SHARP.
THEY'LL KICK US OUT
IF YOU WIN TOO MUCH.
THANKS, MOM,
BUT IF YOU DIDN'T
WANT ME TO WIN,
THEN YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE BROUGHT ME HERE.
EHH...
SAY YOUR PRAYERS.
HUH?
HMM?
AHA!
THANKS FOR THE TIP.
MMHMM!
[NO AUDIO]
QUEEN MAKES 21.
OH, THAT'S JUST FINE!
THAT'S THE WAY
YOU GOT TO FINISH.
YOU MIND
IF I JOIN THE GAME?
HE'S THE ONE.
THAT'S 21.
OH, MAN!
THE TARGET WILL SIT
AT YOUR BLACKJACK TABLE
AND LOSE ALL
OF HIS MONEY.
OF COURSE, YOU'LL USE YOUR
SKILLS TO HELP HIM WITH THAT.
AND HE'LL GIVE YOU
HIS LAST CHIP AS A TIP
A TOKEN FOR
HIS LOVELY DEALER.
THAT'S GREAT.
WHAT ABOUT IT?
PUT THAT CHIP IN MY HANDS,
AND ALL THOSE UGLY DEBTS
OF YOURS WILL DISAPPEAR.
HMM?
THE FINAL HAND.
WHAT A SHAME.
APPEARS I'M NOT SKILLFUL,
AND I'M NOT LUCKY, EITHER.
THEN WHAT ARE YOU?
I SEEM TO BE VERY GENEROUS.
HMM!
ANOTHER BLACKJACK.
YOU CLEANED ME OUT
ALL BUT THIS ONE CHIP.
I THINK I'LL KEEP IT
AS A SOUVENIR.
HUH? HEY, WAIT!
HEY! COME BACK HERE!
[GASPING]
[PANTING]
HUH.
HUH?
HEY, YOU!
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR GENEROSITY?
YOU'RE MESSING UP
THE WHOLE PLAN.
HUH?
DON'T PLAY STUPID.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
GIVE ME THAT LAST CHIP.
YOU'RE PRETTY BRASH.
YOU CHEATED THE WHOLE GAME,
AND I DIDN'T SAY A WORD.
[GASPS]
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
[PEOPLE EXCLAIMING]
NO WONDER I'M BROKE!
UNBELIEVABLE!
JUST GIVE ME THE DAMN CHIP.
OH...
AAH!
CAN YOU COME WITH ME
TO THE OFFICE, SIR?
WE HAVE SOME QUESTIONS.
LIKE WHAT?
BAD MOVE.
HUH?
YOU PUNK!
WHA--?
COME ON, GUYS.
I LIKE THE FITNESS
PROGRAM HERE.
IT'S A GOOD WORKOUT.
[BEEPING]
OK, SHOW TIME.
LOOKS LIKE
WE GOT A PROBLEM.
GOT ANOTHER FIGHT.
OH, A FIGHT, HUH?
HUH?
SPIKE.
YES!
JET!
I TOLD YOU
NOT TO WIN TOO MUCH.
THAT'S NOT IT.
WE GOT TO SPLIT FAST!
COME ON!
I HAVEN'T CASHED
THESE IN YET.
HEY!
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
HE DOESN'T HAVE IT.
THAT CHIP HE WAS CARRYING
IS A FAKE.
NEITHER YOU NOR YOUR BOSS
WERE TOLD WHY
WE COOKED UP THIS PLAN,
BUT THERE'S A REASON,
AND THAT CHIP IS CRUCIAL.
IF IT FALLS INTO POLICE HANDS...
WE'RE FINISHED.
BOSS, WE STILL
CAN'T FIND THE GIRL.
TRACK HER DOWN.
PUT A PRICE
ON HER PRETTY HEAD.
[GUNSHOTS]
WAIT A MINUTE.
I BROUGHT YOU GUYS
BACK HERE.
I SHOULD GET A REWARD
FOR THAT.
WHY ARE YOU LOCKING ME UP?
STUPID DOG!
MY DOG THINKS
YOU SMELL LIKE MONEY,
AND I HAVE
THE VERY SAME IMPRESSION.
WELL, GET OVER IT.
HEY, JET, HOW MUCH DID
YOU WIN ON THOSE SLOTS?
IT MUST HAVE
BEEN 200K, MINIMUM.
AND WHO MADE YOU
LOSE THE WHOLE PILE?
HMM.
200K IS CHUMP CHANGE.
IT'S NOTHING COMPARED
TO WHAT I'VE LOST.
IT'S PEANUTS, AND YOU'RE
BLAMING THE WRONG PERSON!
RIGHT.
YOUR LITTLE ZIPCRAFT
SHOULD SELL FOR AT LEAST 400K.
YOU BROUGHT THIS
ON YOURSELVES.
IF YOU'D GIVEN ME THAT CHIP,
THERE'D HAVE BEEN NO PROBLEM.
--CHIP?
--YEAH, CHIP.
ARE YOU DEAF?
OOH, THAT'S DISGUSTING!
GORDON WILL PAY
A FORTUNE FOR THAT
MORE THAN YOUR
LITTLE BRAIN CAN IMAGINE.
SO WHY DON'T WE CALL HIM?
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I DON'T KNOW
ANYONE NAMED GORDON,
AND EVEN IF I DID,
YOU DON'T REALLY EXPECT ME
TO BUY THAT PHONY STORY,
DO YOU?
WAIT A MINUTE!
COME ON, EIN. LET'S GO.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
COME BACK HERE!
IT'S A CHIP.
OF COURSE IT'S A CHIP.
NOT THE POKER CHIP, DUMMY.
THERE'S ANOTHER CHIP
INSIDE THAT CHIP
A MICROCHIP.
HMM? HMM.
HI, AMIGOS!
YOU READY FOR
SOME BOUNTY INFO?
"BIG SHOT," COWBOYS,
IS COMING YOUR WAY!
WHOA!
SO, COACH,
WHO'S UP FIRST THIS WEEK?
A PRETTY POKER PLAYER
THAT'S HEADED FOR THE POKEY.
YO! HEY, SPIKE!
SHE'S A TOUGH COOKIE
FAYE VALENTINE.
MMM!
AND THE BOUNTY'S A WHOPPING
6 MILLION WOOLONGS.
YO. HEY, JET.
SHUCKS, HOWDY!
HAPPY HUNTING,
ALL YOU COWBOYS.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
FIRST OFF,
I DIDN'T RUN AWAY.
MY SHIP WAS HIJACKED.
I BELIEVE YOU, OF COURSE.
WHERE ARE YOU?
AN OLD FISHING SHIP
AT THE GATE.
AND THEY HAVE
THE CONTROL CHIP, GORDON,
SO HURRY UP AND... HUH?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WELL, WE WERE
THINKING ABOUT YOU,
AND WE HAD
A LITTLE CHANGE OF HEART.
WHY LOCK A FINE
YOUNG LADY LIKE YOU
UP IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
YOU CREEPS AREN'T
GETTING ANY IDEAS, ARE YOU?
ON THE CONTRARY.
WE'RE TAKING YOU SOMEPLACE
WHERE YOU'LL BE
VERY WELL PROTECTED.
OH, AND WHERE
WOULD THAT BE?
THE POLICE STATION.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
200K IS CHUMP CHANGE COMPARED
TO YOUR PRICE, FAYE VALENTINE.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
DID THEY PUT A BOUNTY ON ME?
6 MILLION FAT WOOLONGS.
6 MILLION?
IS THAT ALL
THEY'RE OFFERING?
JUST HOW MUCH MONEY
DO YOU OWE, ANYWAY?
COME ON.
HAVE A HEART.
TAKE ME ANYWHERE BUT THE POLICE.
THEY'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO WILL PAY YOUR BOUNTY.
I CAN'T BE STUCK
IN ONE PLACE FOR LONG.
IT WILL KILL ME.
MY WHOLE FAMILY'S LIKE THAT.
YEAH, RIGHT.
WE'RE ROMANIES.
FOR EONS, WE'VE WANDERED
THE STARS, LOOKING FOR LOVE.
IT'S OUR WAY.
HUH?
YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING, DO YOU?
ROMANIES ARE GYPSIES.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT WE CALL
SOMEONE LIKE YOU?
A GAUJO.
THAT MEANS A BUMPKIN WHO
DOESN'T KNOW WHICH WAY IS UP.
GAUJO. I LIKE THAT.
[HOWLS]
THE WILDS ARE CALLING ME!
YOU CAN'T KEEP ME LOCKED UP!
SAVE IT FOR THE POLICE.
COME ON, JET.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
OH, FINE!
LOOK, I'M NOT GOING TO RUN AWAY!
AT LEAST UNCUFF ONE HAND.
I CAN'T EVEN GO
TO THE BATHROOM THIS WAY!
MAN, YOU'RE
A REAL TALKER, AREN'T YOU?
SPIKE, MY FRIEND,
THAT GIRL IS MONEY IN THE BANK.
YEAH. NO PENALTY
FOR EARLY WITHDRAWAL.
IT'S JUST LIKE
CHARLIE SAID IN MY DREAM.
IF YOU WANT TO RECEIVE,
YOU HAVE TO GIVE.
SEE, SPIKE?
YOU GOT TO LISTEN
TO YOUR DREAMS.
THAT'S HOW YOU'LL FIND
YOUR DREAM GIRL.
[CRASH]
HEY!
OW!
WHO'S THAT?
I'M NOT SURE WHO YOU ARE,
AND I DON'T REALLY GIVE A DAMN.
YOU HAVE MY CHIP,
AND I WANT IT BACK.
WELL, I'M NOT
SURE WHO YOU ARE,
AND I'M NOT GIVING
YOU ANYTHING.
ARE WE DONE NOW?
IT'S JUST A POKER CHIP.
IT HAS NO VALUE TO YOU.
OH, WE'VE BECOME
QUITE FOND OF IT,
AND WE KNOW WHAT IT'S WORTH.
3 YEARS AGO, S.I.T. DEVELOPED
A MASTER DECRYPTION PROGRAM
CALLED CRYPTBREAKER.
RUMOR HAS IT THAT SHORTLY
AFTER ITS COMPLETION,
THE PROGRAMMER TURNED UP DEAD
AND THE PROGRAM DISAPPEARED
A PROGRAM WITH ADVANCED
ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE.
IT CAN DECRYPT AND UNLOCK
VIRTUALLY ANY SECURITY CODE.
BUT THE CATCH IS,
THE PROGRAM ITSELF IS ENCODED.
SO WHOEVER HAS IT
NEEDS THE KEY TO OPEN IT
THE KEY TO THE KEY,
SO TO SPEAK.
THEY SAY THE COPS
AND THE I.S.S.P. SPECIAL FORCES
HAVE BEEN SEARCHING EVERY
CORNER OF THE ASTEROIDS FOR IT.
GUESS THEY NEVER THOUGHT
TO LOOK IN A CASINO.
OR EVEN IF THEY DID, WHO'D EVER
SUSPECT A HUMBLE POKER CHIP?
HMM. NOT BAD.
YOU'VE DONE YOUR HOMEWORK.
I USED TO BE WITH I.S.S.P.
SPECIAL FORCES MYSELF,
IN ANOTHER LIFETIME.
OF COURSE, A CASINO
IS A PERFECT PLACE
TO LAUNDER LARGE SUMS
OF STOLEN MONEY.
YOU HAD THE RIGHT IDEA.
YOU JUST CHOSE THE WRONG DAY.
NOW, IT'S ONLY RIGHT
THAT WE DO OUR CIVIC DUTY
AND GIVE IT TO THE POLICE,
SINCE, AS YOU POINTED OUT,
IT'S WORTHLESS TO US.
IT'S NOT WORTHLESS
IF I PAY YOU FOR IT.
300 MILLION WOOLONGS?
NAH, I'LL GO EASY ON YOU.
MAKE IT 30 MILLION.
CHEAP FOR A MAGIC KEY, HUH?
ALL RIGHT.
OK. 6 MILLION
TURNS INTO 30 MILLION.
OUR LITTLE NEST
EGG'S GROWING.
JUST BE READY.
DON'T GET CAUGHT OFF GUARD.
OKEY-DOKEY.
HUH?
[DOG GROWLING]
SHH!
[DOG BARKING]
STUPID DOG!
SELLERS WHO WANT CASH UP
FRONT ARE RARE THESE DAYS.
YEAH. GUESS I'M JUST
AN OLDFASHIONED KIND OF GUY.
BEAUTIFUL.
NOW, WE WILL BOTH COUNT TO 3.
THEN WE'LL RELEASE
THE MAGNETIC FIELD
AND MOVE IT UP TOWARD YOU.
AT THE EXACT SAME TIME,
YOU WILL TOSS THE CHIP
CAREFULLY TO US.
NO PROBLEM.
I'M TRUSTING YOU, PAL.
CONFIRM THAT WE HAVE THE CHIP,
THEN DESTROY THEM.
RIGHT.
LET'S DO IT.
1...2...3.
HUH?
[CRASH]
HEY!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO OPEN THE HANGAR!
OH!
AAH!
HUH?
HEY, GAUJO.
HELLO, ROMANY.
--BYE.
--DON'T LET HER GO.
FIRE!
SHIT!
JET, GET ME OUT OF HERE!
ALL RIGHT!
SINK THEM!
DESTROY ALL OF THEM!
NO WAY.
SHE REVERSED POLARITY
ON ONE OF THE MISSILES!
IT'S COMING BACK AROUND!
AAH!
SHE BEAT ME AGAIN.
ALL THIS THING
IS GOOD FOR NOW IS ONE BET.
MIGHT AS WELL USE IT.
WE'RE STARTING
FROM SQUARE ONE.
HEY, THE DEALER'S CHEATING!
THIS SUCKS.
THIS WORLD'S A MESS.
ECONOMIC RECESSION,
KIDS BLOWING THEIR MINDS.
YOU BEEN READING
THE PAPER AGAIN?
TAKE A LOOK AT THE BEBOP.
IT'S A BIGGER MESS
THAN THAT.
BAH! THAT'S NOTHING.
CHECK OUT THIS NEWS REPORT.
INTERGALACTIC TERRORISTS
THEY WANT TO BLOW UP GANYMEDE.
HUH?
THEY'RE ENVIRONMENTAL
PROTECTIONISTS.
PERFECT.
THEY CAN GET RID OF
THIS FURBALL YOU CALL A DOG.
NEXT EPISODE, GATEWAY SHUFFLE.
MAN, I'M LOSING IT.