♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1.
LET'S JAM. ♪
CONFIRMED.
TO THE NEW ALLIANCE,
AND PERHAPS EVEN FRIENDSHIP.
AND TO SUCCESS
FOR BOTH OF US.
I HAD NO IDEA
THE VIEW FROM UP HERE
WOULD BE SO BREATHTAKING.
IT MAKES ME SAD TO LEAVE.
THE NEXT TIME,
YOU'LL HAVE TO STAY FOR DINNER.
OUR CHEF COOKS
A CANTONESE CUISINE
THAT'S JUST AS SUPERB
AS THE SCENERY.
IT'S TO DIE FOR,
SO TO SPEAK.
THAT'S QUITE AN INVITATION.
I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D BREAK BREAD WITH A CAPO
FROM THE RED DRAGON CLAN.
DON'T WORRY.
THE FOOD WON'T BE POISONED.
NO MORE BETRAYALS.
THANK GOD I CAN FINALLY RELAX,
TAKE A LITTLE BREATHER.
[BIRD SQUAWKING]
THIS WON'T DO YOU ANY GOOD.
THE TIMES HAVE CHANGED.
THE SYNDICATES CAN'T
SURVIVE LIKE THIS ANY LONGER.
THIS ENDLESS BLOODLETTING
IS TEARING US ALL APART.
[GASPS]
IF SPIKE WERE HERE...
YOU WOULD NEVER HAVE DONE THIS.
I DON'T FEEL UP FOR THIS.
[WHINES]
HUH?
I SAID, I DON'T FEEL
LIKE DOING THIS.
THEN I HAVE NO CHOICE.
HOLD ON A MINUTE, SPIKE.
HEY, I DON'T WANT
TO BOTHER YOU.
DON'T GET SALTY, ALL RIGHT?
JUST HOW MUCH DO YOU
KNOW ABOUT THESE BOYS?
ENOUGH TO GET THE PICTURE.
WELL, THEN?
THERE'S A FAT BOUNTY,
PLENTY OF INFO ON THE GUY,
AND WE HAVE A LEAD.
SO WHAT ARE YOU SCARED OF?
SPIKE, YOU'RE AVOIDING
THE SUBJECT, AND YOU KNOW IT.
WHAT ARE TRYING
TO HIDE FROM ME?
SO HOW'D YOU MESS UP
YOUR ARM, HUH, JET?
WHAT DOES THAT
HAVE TO DO WITH IT?
NOTHING AT ALL.
SO WHEN ARE YOU GOING
TO ANSWER MY QUESTION?
WHEN YOU ANSWER MINE.
WHY IS THIS DOOR SO SMALL?
YOU CAN HARDLY GET THROUGH.
UH, WHAT'S GOING ON?
NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
HMM. HEY!
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
A TEAM HERE, YOU KNOW.
SINCE WHEN?
YOU'RE JUST WALKING TROUBLE,
SO STAY OUT OF IT.
HMM. FINE.
LIKE I CARE.
SO WHO'S THIS GUY? NEW HIT?
ASK BEFORE YOU LOOK.
IT'S SITTING RIGHT THERE.
LIGHTEN UP.
SPIKE!
WAIT A MINUTE, SPIKE!
PREPARE FOR TAKEOFF.
SPIKE! JERK.
I'M NOT GOING TO BACK YOU UP.
YOUR CALL.
DAMN IT!
BULLHEADED.
MAO YENRAI.
A 28 MILLION BOUNTY
FOR MURDERING A CRIME BOSS.
HE'S THE HEAD
OF A SYNDICATE, HUH?
WHOA!
THAT'S WHO YOU GUYS ARE AFTER?
WHAT? YOU HAVE A FIGHT?
CAN IT!
YOU'RE BEING OBNOXIOUS.
HMM. REALLY?
I SAID, CAN IT!
HE CAN DO WHATEVER
THE HELL HE WANTS.
OH, GOD.
MEN ARE SUCH BABIES.
HMM?
ARE YOU THERE, JET?
I'VE GOT SOMETHING BIG!
SOMETHING BIG? HMM.
MADAM, EXCUSE ME.
I NEED TO SEE YOUR TICKET
FOR THE CONCERT, PLEASE.
TICKET?
OH, I DON'T HAVE ANY TICKET.
WELL, THEN I'M AFRAID
I CAN'T LET YOU IN, MADAM.
ALL RIGHT, BUT HE'S GOING
TO BE VERY UNHAPPY WITH YOU.
HUH?
THAT'S RIGHT, HIM.
BALCONY, FIRST BOX.
YOU KNOW WHO.
OH! MAO YENR--
CAN YOU PARK MY ZIPCRAFT?
IT'S OUT FRONT.
THANKS.
OH! MMM.
WHAT MAKES THEM ALL THINK
THEY CAN DO WHATEVER
THE HELL THEY LIKE?
HUH?
THERE'S AN ENCRYPTION
ON THIS THING.
[WHINES]
HMM? YOU WORRIED?
RELAX.
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN
THE DECRYPTION MASTER AT WORK.
YOU SEE?
NOW WE TYPE IN "MAO YENRAI."
SO I WAS RIGHT.
THE BOUNTY'S FOR REAL,
BUT THERE'S A WHOLE LOT
MORE TO IT.
[ORCHESTRA PLAYING]
[MAN SINGING "AVE MARIA"]
IS THIS MR. MAO YENRAI'S BOX?
I LOOKED ALL OVER FOR IT.
ACTUALLY, I--
YES. WE'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR YOU.
[GASPS]
UNH!
WE REQUEST THAT YOU REMAIN
QUIET DURING THE PERFORMANCE.
HMM.
PUT 'EM BACK!
YOU'RE NOT GETTING AWAY!
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
HMM?
HUH?
HEY, GIVE IT BACK,
YOU DUMBASS!
GIMME!
OOH.
REALLY! KIDS THESE DAYS!
I'LL HAND YOU BOTH
OVER TO THE POLICE!
OH, MY DEAR GOD.
HEY.
[KIDS GIGGLE]
UH...
ISN'T IT BAD FOR YOUR HEALTH
TO DRINK IT ALL
IN ONE GULP, ANNIE?
WHAT'S BAD FOR MY HEALTH
IS SEEING YOU
COME BACK TO LIFE.
IT'S A SHOCK TO THE SYSTEM.
HEY, THANKS A LOT
FOR THE WARM WELCOME.
HMM! WHY WELCOME THE DEAD?
IT'S ALL FUTILE.
BUT I'M ALIVE.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
YOU DIED 3 YEARS AGO.
THAT'S HOW THINGS WORK HERE.
I KNOW WHY
YOU'RE HERE, SPIKE.
HUH?
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE COME UNLESS
YOU NEEDED SOME INFORMATION,
SOMETHING IMPORTANT, RIGHT?
WELL, I'LL HELP IF I CAN,
BUT DON'T ASK ME TOO MUCH.
ANASTASIA.
NO! DON'T YOU CALL ME THAT!
THERE ARE ONLY TWO PEOPLE
WHO CAN USE THAT NAME.
SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO KNOW?
MAO YENRAI,
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
[MAN SINGING "AVE MARIA"]
MAO TAIJIN,
WHAT'S THE REASON FOR THIS?
NO NEED TO SPEAK,
MISS... VALENTINE.
[GASPS]
WE'VE DONE A VERY THOROUGH
BACKGROUND CHECK ON YOU.
[GASPS]
REST ASSURED, YOU'LL BE HELD
IN A VERY SECURE LOCATION.
PLEASE, TAKE YOUR SEAT.
OH.
YOU'RE TREMBLING.
WHO ARE YOU?
TELL ME!
VICIOUS.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T
TELL YOU WHAT TO DO,
BUT JUST DON'T GET TANGLED UP
WITH VICIOUS ANYMORE, RIGHT?
WHY AM I TALKING TO YOU?
IT'S USELESS.
SORRY.
YOU'VE NEVER LISTENED
TO ANYONE IN YOUR WHOLE LIFE.
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
YOU'RE A STUBBORN SHOWOFF!
YOU THINK IT'D KILL YOU
TO LISTEN TO YOUR
ELDERS FOR ONCE?
NO, THAT'S TOO MUCH TO ASK.
ABOUT MAO, HE HAD A LOT
OF GUYS OUT LOOKING FOR YOU.
HE WAS CONVINCED
YOU WERE STILL ALIVE
SAID HE COULD FEEL IT.
NO ONE COULD
TALK HIM OUT OF IT.
SO NOW HERE YOU ARE,
FINALLY BACK, AND MAO IS...
ANNIE, I THINK
YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH.
NOT YET.
THIS ONE'S FOR MAO.
IF IT'S FOR MAO,
THEN I'LL DRINK IT MYSELF.
ALL RIGHT, AND WHAT
ARE YOU PLANNING
TO DO WITH
ALL THE ARTILLERY?
WHERE'S THE GIRL?
WHEN SHE SAW THE BOUNTY FIGURE,
SHE HAD A LAPSE OF SANITY.
I'M SURE SHE'S OUT SOMEWHERE
SCREWING UP
AND GETTING IN TROUBLE.
I SEE.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GET
ANY REWARD MONEY FOR MAO.
HE'S ALREADY DEAD...
ASSASSINATED.
INTERNAL POLITICS BETWEEN
RIVAL CRIME SYNDICATES,
YOU UNDERSTAND?
IT'S A TRAP!
YEAH, I KNOW.
I KNOW THE WHOLE SAD STORY.
AND YOU'RE STILL GOING?
WAIT. DOES THIS
HAVE TO DO WITH MAO?
YEAH. I HAVE
A DEBT TO PAY OFF.
YOU WANTED TO KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO MY ARM.
HUH?
THIS IS WHAT I PAID,
YEAH, FOR BEING TOO GUNGHO
AND RUNNING AHEAD OF THE GAME.
YOU GET THE POINT?
I DON'T WANT
TO DO THIS, JET.
THEN WHY ARE YOU?
LET'S JUST SAY MY PAST
IS CATCHING UP TO ME.
[BEEPING]
I KIND OF GOT MYSELF CAUGHT.
WHA--?
YEAH. THEY WANT YOU
TO COME AND PICK ME UP.
EITHER YOU SHOW UP
AT THE PLACE THEY SPECIFY,
OR MY LIFE IS OVER.
OH, THE ARRIVAL TIME IS--
WHO ASKED YOU
TO GO OFF ON YOUR OWN?
AW, COME ON, NOW!
WE'RE COMRADES, RIGHT?
YOU BROUGHT THIS ON YOURSELF,
SO DEAL WITH IT YOURSELF.
WE'RE BUSY.
NO! WAIT, JET!
--HUH?
--WHERE ARE YOU?
HUH?
YOU MEAN YOU'RE REALLY
GOING TO COME FOR ME?
WELL, IT'S POSSIBLE.
I'VE GOT MY REASONS,
SO DON'T TAKE IT PERSONAL.
SPIKE!
♪ I DON'T FEEL A THING ♪
♪ AND I STOPPED REMEMBERING ♪
♪ THE DAYS ARE JUST LIKE
MOMENTS TURNED TO HOURS ♪
♪ MOTHER USED TO SAY ♪
♪ IF YOU WANT,
YOU'LL FIND A WAY ♪
♪ BUT MOTHER NEVER DANCED
THROUGH FIRE SHOWERS ♪
♪ WALK IN THE RAIN ♪
♪ IN THE RAIN ♪
♪ I WALK IN THE RAIN ♪
♪ IS IT RIGHT ♪
♪ OR IS IT WRONG? ♪
♪ AND IS IT HERE
THAT I BELONG? ♪
WHEN ANGELS
ARE FORCED OUT OF HEAVEN,
THEY BECOME DEVILS.
YOU AGREE, DON'T YOU, SPIKE?
I'M JUST WATCHING A BAD DREAM
I NEVER WAKE UP FROM.
I'LL WAKE YOU UP RIGHT NOW.
WHAT'S YOUR RUSH, VICIOUS?
AFTER ALL,
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
ARE YOU PLEADING
FOR YOUR LIFE?
HARDLY.
BEGGING DOESN'T
WORK ON YOU, REMEMBER?
EVEN IF IT'S COMING
FROM A MAN WHO TOOK YOU IN
AND MADE YOU WHAT YOU ARE.
PERHAPS, BUT HE WAS A BEAST
WHO LOST HIS FANGS.
THAT'S WHY HE HAD
TO DIE, SPIKE.
AND THAT'S WHY
YOU HAVE TO DIE.
[WOMAN GASPS]
♪ FOR SOME REASON,
I THINK OF HOME ♪
NOW, WE'D LIKE YOU
TO DROP THE GUN SLOWLY.
WHAT'S WRONG?
IF YOU DON'T COMPLY...
BE CAREFUL!
HUH? OH!
I'M BUTCHERING IT.
[BEEPING]
HUH?
HELLO?
OH, GOD!
JET! IT'S SPIKE, HE'S--
TOUGH!
DAMN IT!
YOU SHOULD SEE YOURSELF.
YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE
RIGHT AT THIS MOMENT, SPIKE?
WHAT?
A RAVENOUS BEAST.
THE SAME BLOOD
RUNS THROUGH BOTH OF US,
THE BLOOD OF A BEAST
WHO WANDERS,
HUNTING FOR
THE BLOOD OF OTHERS.
I'VE BLED ALL
THAT KIND OF BLOOD AWAY.
THEN WHY ARE
YOU STILL ALIVE?
[WOMAN HUMMING]
JUST LIKE THAT.
SING FOR ME, PLEASE.
[WOMAN HUMMING]
HUH? OH!
YOU'RE FINALLY UP, HUH?
YOU SLEPT TOO MUCH.
YOU'VE BEEN ASLEEP 3 DAYS.
YEAH.
I WAS STARTING
TO WORRY ABOUT YOU.
HEY, YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL
TO ME FOR STAYING HERE.
[MUFFLED SPEECH]
HMM? OH.
HUH?
YOU SING OFF KEY.
OW!
HUH?
OH, WELL.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS HAS BECOME A WORLD
WITH NO INTEGRITY.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
EVERYONE'S PUTTING A LID
ON SOMETHING THAT SMELLS.
YEAH?
AND WE LET IT HAPPEN.
COULD YOU TELL ME
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT?
THE WORLD WHAT'S
GOING ON IN THE WORLD.
WITH ALL THESE LIDS, THE WORLD
IS GOING TO BE BURIED IN LIDS.
YOU LOST ME, BUD.
THEY KEEP US
FROM SEEING THE TRUTH.
TRUTH, HUH?
YEAH. IT'S ALL THOSE LIDS.
I'M GOING TO CRUSH
THEM ALL AWAY.
NEXT EPISODE,
SYMPATHY FOR THE DEVIL.
SOUNDS SMELLY.