♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
TO BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1.
LET'S JAM. ♪
[FOOTSTEPS]
HELLO, GENTLEMEN.
I JOURNEYED HERE
IN ORDER TO TAKE YOUR LIVES.
[GUNSHOTS]
HELLO, BOY.
NAY.
[CAT MEOWING]
[SIRENS]
YOUR PARTNER RAN
INTO SOME VERY BAD LUCK, JET.
WELL, HE NEVER HAD ANY
GOOD LUCK IN THE FIRST PLACE.
YEAH, BUT THIS IS REAL BAD.
IF YOU'RE SMART,
YOU'LL STAY OUT OF IT.
I DON'T CARE.
JUST TELL ME WHAT'S UP.
LISTEN. I'M TELLING YOU THIS
FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
AND IF YOU GET INVOLVED
IN THIS,
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE A WORLD
OF TROUBLE FOR ME.
YOU KNOW, BOB,
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE I CAN
TURN TO FOR HELP RIGHT NOW.
I'LL MAKE SURE IT DOESN'T CAUSE
ANY PROBLEMS FOR YOU.
WHERE HAVE I HEARD THAT BEFORE?
YOU'RE ALWAYS IN TROUBLE, JET.
ANYONE CLOSE TO YOU
GETS DRAGGED IN.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS ONLY A RUMOR,
BUT HAVE YOU HEARD OF
THE NAME MAD PIERROT?
SO THE RUMOR'S TRUE.
WE HAVE A MUMMY ON THE SHIP.
I HEARD YOU GOT BEAT UP
BY SOME FREAKY GUY, SPIKE.
JUST LEAVE ME
THE HELL ALONE, WILL YOU?
I SEEM TO RECALL YOU BEING
IN THIS CONDITION BEFORE.
YOU'RE NOT SHOWING
A WHOLE LOT OF IMPROVEMENT,
BUT NOT A LOT I CAN
DO ABOUT IT, HUH?
[MUMBLING]
LET'S FACE IT.
YOU END UP LIKE THIS BECAUSE
YOU GO LOOKING FOR TROUBLE.
IT'S CALLED BAD BEHAVIOR.
BUT NOT MY PROBLEM, HUH?
HMM.
[MUMBLING]
WELL, SINCE THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO ABOUT IT,
I'LL BE OFF. TAKE CARE.
THE VICTIM WAS A HIGHRANKING
DIRECTOR AT I.S.S.P.,
THE SEVENTH ONE TO GO DOWN.
WHAT?
I DON'T BLAME YOU
FOR BEING SURPRISED.
THEY'VE KEPT IT
A TIGHT SECRET.
THE TOP GUYS
DEFINITELY DON'T WANT
THE WORLD TO KNOW ABOUT THIS.
WHY IS THAT?
YOUR PARTNER
IS IN DEEP TROUBLE.
THIS GUY'S A PERFECT
KILLING MACHINE.
THEY SAY THAT NOBODY
WHO'S SEEN HIS FACE
HAS LIVED TO TELL ABOUT IT.
THOSE FEW THAT
MANAGED TO GET AWAY
WERE HUNTED DOWN RELENTLESSLY,
AND THEY ALWAYS TURNED UP DEAD.
THEY SAY HE APPEARS
WITH A SMILE,
AND HE LEAVES WITH A SMILE.
YEAH, HE'S A MYSTERY,
ALL RIGHT.
AN ASSASSIN KNOWN
AS MAD PIERROT TONGPU.
[LAUGHING]
[BEEPING]
[WHINE]
[BARKING]
[YAWNING]
FAYEFAYE, SMOKESMOKE,
FAYEFAYE.
PUFFPUFF, FAYEFAYE.
MY NAME'S FAYE,
NOT FAYEFAYE.
JUST SAY IT ONCE, OK?
FAYEFAYE, SOME WEIRD MAIL
CAMECAME FOR BEBOPBEBOP.
I WOULD HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO PAY IT OFF
IF I HAD JUST
A LITTLE MORE TIME.
WOULD YOU HOLD STILL? HMM.
"HELLO, BOY. YOU'RE INVITED
TO A WONDERFUL PARTY."
WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS IS-- ALL RIGHT,
DON'T TELL SPIKE ABOUT THIS.
IT'S A SECRET, OK?
BUT WHY? FAYEFAYE,
WHY KEEP IT A SECRET?
IF WE DON'T,
THAT LUNKHEAD
WILL RUN RIGHT OUT
TO THE PARTY?
IT'S SECRET MAILMAIL
FROM MARS.
IT'S SPACELAND.
NICE PLACE TO HOLD A PARTY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
YEAH. YOU GONNA GO
LIKE THAT?
IT'S PERFECT FOR A MASQUERADE,
ISN'T IT?
MAYBE THIS IS THE ONE,
THE ONE I WON'T COME BACK
FROM, THE END.
JUST PLAYING WITH YOUR HEAD.
WOULD YOU RESCUE ME
IF IT WERE TRUE?
LUNKHEAD.
LUNKHEAD, LUNKHEAD, LUNKHEAD!
[LAUGHS]
[BEEPING]
HEY, ED.
UHHUH?
WAKE UP. WHERE'S SPIKE?
HE WENT SOMEWHERE.
WHAT? NOT THAT THIS
IS ANYTHING NEW, OF COURSE.
THAT LUNKHEAD.
LUNKHEAD, LUNKHEAD!
ED, I NEED A FAVOR.
WHAT? WHAT?
[GRUNTING]
[BELL RINGS]
HELLO! WELCOME!
YO.
[LAUGHS]
LET'S PARTY!
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING]
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED IN HERE.
IT'S DANGEROUS IN HERE.
LET'S PLAY OUTSIDE.
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED.
SHUT UP!
LET'S PLAY OUTSIDE.
IT'S DANGEROUS IN HERE.
IT'S DANGEROUS.
LET'S PLAY OUTSIDE.
HI!
[LAUGHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
AAH!
ALL RIGHT, ED,
FIRST INSTRUCTION
ENTER THE I.S.S.P. MAINFRAME
AND DO A SEARCH FOR SECTION 13.
YOU FOLLOW ME?
AYEAYE!
EDWARD, AS FAR AS
THE PUBLIC'S CONCERNED,
THAT SECTION
DOESN'T EVEN EXIST.
IT'S TIGHTLY SECURED.
CAN YOU HACK INTO IT?
YES.
[LAUGHTER]
[LAUGHTER CONTINUES]
HELLO.
[VOICE BOX MALFUNCTIONING]
I FOUND IT!
OK. GOOD.
TRY TO GET IN AND LOCATE A FILE
WITH THE CODENAME TONGPU.
TONGPU. TONGPU.
[LAUGHTER]
[GRUNTS]
[LAUGHING]
PEEKABOO.
I SEE YOU. HA HA.
I.S.S.P. ASSASSINATION SKILLS
ENHANCEMENT EXPERIMENT.
CLINICAL TRIAL SAMPLE
CHART NUMBER 46.
CODENAME: TONGPU.
CONFIRMED.
A MARKED REGRESSION
OF THE MIND OCCURRED
DURING ENHANCEMENT
DEVELOPMENT PROCESS.
EXPERIMENT CANCELED.
SAMPLE TO BE PERMANENTLY
MAINTAINED
AT QUARANTINED FACILITY.
IN THE BEGINNING,
HE ESCAPED FROM THE FACILITY
TO SEEK REVENGE,
BUT NOW HE SEEMS TO ACTUALLY
ENJOY THE ACT OF KILLING.
APPARENTLY HIS MIND
IS CONTINUING TO REGRESS,
SO HE'S LIKE A CHILD WITH
SUPERHUMAN COMBAT CAPABILITIES.
AND REALLY THERE'S NOTHING
MORE PURE AND CRUEL AS A CHILD.
IT'S SHOWTIME!
[LAUGHING]
THAT'S THE LAST THING I NEED.
HELLO. HELLO.
HI.
[LAUGHTER]
[MEOWING]
[SCREAMING]
[CRYING]
MOMMY! MOMMY, IT HURTS!
[CRYING AND SCREAMING]
MOMMY!
MAMA!
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
SPIKE, LISTEN.
WE FIGURED OUT
WHAT HE IS. HE'S A--
FORGET IT. I DON'T
NEED THE INFO ANYMORE.
MAN, I HATE THEME PARKS.
I KNEW SOMETHING FISHY
WAS GOING ON.
SO THAT'S WHAT IT WAS.
HUH? WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU CAN'T REALLY JUDGE
A PERSON BY THEIR LOOKS.
HONESTLY DISGUSTING.
WHOA! WHOA!
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
I NEVER THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
A TEENAGE GIRL.
MAKES ME DESPISE HIM.
WHO ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
NEXT EPISODE
BOOGIE WOOGIE FENG SHUI.
AW, I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING
FOR THE WHOLE PREVIEW.