Yes, human suffering.
It's such a unique privilege,
isn't it?
Hey, dick cop, don't take
the little chickie away
from the party so soon!
Come on. She'd like it more
if she went bye bye with me!
A big brother's protection
extends from womb to tomb,
and therefore-
Today, there is
a new development
in the antirobot movement.
We have received official
confirmation from the MPD
of a definite connection
between the
Kelly McCanon incident,
the terrorist puppet bombings,
and the recent massacre
at the hospital in Shinora.
The police are asking
for our viewers' help
in locating these two suspects:
Ross Sylibus and Naomi Armitage.
The MPD confirmed there
is a definite connection.
If you have any information,
please notify the police.
Let me pick out our next
meeting place, okay?
Tables, with umbrellas.
If that makes you too sick,
I know a vending machine
and a clean bench.
I guess maybe this
is the worst place.
The worst place?
Only if I was in your shoes.
Will you cut the crap!
Did you find anything?
Yeah, your Danich Hill exists,
but not on any map.
Found a good highway going
smack blank into a mountain,
but there's no Asakura
address box inviting any mail
from a rogue cop.
No sati-topographicals?
C'mon! Like I really
got a couple of moons
to power this thing.
Hey, what're you doin'?
A loss, in duty.
Yeah, the dearly departed.
Hey, Ross!
Can you tell those guys...
the Martians, tell
'em Eddie says "What's up?"
I will.
So, what's wrong?
Well, are you gonna tell me?
Are you O.K.?
No, I'm not.
My CPU's all messed up.
They say the mind's
the first thing to go.
Humans say it.
Come on, machines
don't go senile.
They also say life
is pretty short.
It's like an
expiration date, you know?
Hey, how come?
What?
What's the reason
you're doing all this for me?
How come you're still
hanging around with me?
And driving me
all the way out here?
Why change from
a good cop to a criminal?
How come-
Stop it! You're asking stupid
questions like some little kid.
Why? How come?
There's no answer.
Huh?
That's it, isn't it?
Coordinates.
Virgin? Yeah,
maybe if you just landed.
Hey, it wastes fuel
to keep the motor running.
Yo, anybody here?
We're looking for
a guy called Asakura.
Is anyone here?
You got visitors!
Huh?
What happened?
Alright, take it easy.
Move away from it nice and slow.
Don't shoot!
It's only a robot.
Yeah, a big one.
It's somehow just like me.
I think it's a bioroid type.
What is it, some
kind of a prototype?
May I help you?
Huh?
Talk about your family trees.
It's just another robot.
Just like the giant.
I heard someone calling
for Dr. Asakura.
Uh, I did.
Appointment?
No, I suppose not.
Would you follow me, please?
Dr. Asakura, visitors! A Mr...
Sylibus.
Papa!
The new man from Conception!
It's been so many years,
and you even brought one
of the models along.
Mr. Sylibus.
Uh, but I'm not-
Papa!
Oh, but she's only a Third.
She's so inferior.
The poor little thing,
but you needn't be so kind.
It's outdated.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Here, take a look at this.
A fourth type that
Conception can be proud of.
There's no longer any need to
copy humans or plants anymore.
They live. They're ALIVEs!
Oh, no, we should
call them "phobians."
What? Yes, a new life, my
Marforteans, but you won't.
You'll just be calling
them anything you want
when you market them.
The stupid company you work
for is just going to call them
the Fourths aren't they?
They're ALIVEs!
A grand conception!
Then it all goes wrong.
The doctor's mind was
unfortunately altered.
Reduplication of his
thoughts is very difficult.
Please, be patient.
His memory, was it erased?
Who are you?
I am Wilbur D'anclaude
and Dr. Asakura's aide.
Oh, well yeah he might look
to you like he's one of those
damn assassinroids,
but I fixed up his crazy head,
just as you can see.
Indeed he did.
The violent tendencies I had are
now gone, due to the upgrade.
What's the reason?
Pardon?
Dr. Asakura. His mind,
just what's wrong with it?
Forget it, Ross.
That's enough.
Are you still cold?
It's affecting
my nervous system.
I'm sorry I lost my temper,
I was just hoping that the
doctor could help you somehow.
Never count on hope.
You'll lose.
When wishes are gone,
hope gives nothing.
And then you hope that
your father might know.
And hopes are really fragile.
They get all ruined,
every time you believe
that some one else
is gonna help your
hopes come true.
A hope is a feeling.
Maybe you'll be okay.
If I was a Second, then
I wouldn't even be able
to think of all
this stupid crap.
But I'm programmed
to be a human,
and I don't know what it means.
Hope is a human feeling,
isn't it?
Come on, tell me more-
Hey, I met one. He's a human,
and he's less real than all of
the things you're talking about.
Know what he said?
Don't give up.
Ross.
Are you sure?
Oh, Armitage.
I think it's the only thing I've
been sure of since I got here.
How 'bout you?
Well, at least something
is normal here on Mars.
But I'm not normal.
I'm a robot.
I'm half robot, too.
But I know a true heart
when I've met one.
We interrupt this broadcast
for the following announcement:
Good evening,
we've just received word that
as of 11:00 PM, UTN time,
the economic agreement
has been signed at last.
Mars and Earth have
finally signed the treaty.
Officials from both powers
are quoted as saying,
"This is a first step toward
one world, one nation."
Follow me, there's something
I'd like to show you.
Where's the doc?
This morning,
he's with his ALIVEs.
He's concentrating on
further hybridization.
He intends to continue
and complete the initial
terraforming plans.
That isn't possible.
Yes, rational
thought would agree.
Don't worry. The unborn
sister poses no threat.
Dr. Asakura gave up
weapon production.
He left this new model
unfinished. But why?
A difference of opinion with his
partner Professor D'anclaude?
I... that's enough.
Let's go.
Is there something else?
I brought you here, because I
felt you had previous knowledge
of the Thirds being
created as assassinroids.
Nice, upgrade. Go on.
It's the unfinished work.
Professor D'anclaude began
work on female assassinroids,
which would some way compliment
the multitude of my brothers.
Along with myself and Armitage,
we were the pinnacle
of robotic creation.
Although our strength and
abilities far surpassed humans,
it was quite simple
to assimilate ourselves
into their society.
Then, Dr. Asakura used us as
a base of synthetic organisms
in developing the Thirds.
Programming creativity and
life instead of the directive
to destroy.
Unfortunately, all the
prototypes had an imperfection.
There were many instabilities
within the logic boards
of the Third CPU.
Of course, Dr. Asakura's present
state of mind prevented him
from ever quite perfecting
the female models.
I'm nothing.
He couldn't finish. I'm useless!
He doesn't even care!
No, wait!
So, why create a Third type?
I mean, the Seconds were
good enough, even on Earth.
Perhaps being from Earth, you
do not have the knowledge of
the difficulties there are
with low Martian birthrates.
No. I've heard.
What's it mean?
Any colony desiring
independence,
requires a populace.
Otherwise, they can't
develop a new identity.
And Mars will continue to be
weak, as long as it remains
dependent on the Earth
for its immigration.
So what about Conception?
There's gotta be more to it than
just the money that's involved.
Indeed, manufacturers of
Thirds, which can give birth,
gain strength
through numbers.
The more people they represent,
the stronger their
position grows.
Logical. But then the
assassinations make no sense.
They do. If you're the
government and hope to sign
a treaty with the
Earth Federation.
Nah, they couldn't.
Do you think they've
really done it?
Mars has no other recourse.
The Earth Federation
is now strongly feminist.
A robot who can conceive,
contradicts the basis of
the Terran Party's position
of basic humanity.
For Mars to agree, Mars
must eliminate the Thirds.
They are now an obstruction.
Is that what you think?
That I'm just old Martian
garbage to be thrown out?
You're wrong.
I'm gonna stay alive
for as long I can-
Exactly, your programming
for self-preservation
is exactly equal to ours
for eliminating your kind.
But I am now refined.
Unlike my brothers, I respect
your wish for continued life.
Hey Eddie.
He's on suspension for aiding
a fugitive, section 10.
No, not if I forced him into it.
Perhaps he'll be pardoned.
I'll submit it.
This Danich Hill Dome
has become a military
attack point.
The government has made their
own connections between you two
and the second puppet bombings.
This is an official notice.
You're a threat
to the government,
the MPD officially renounces
all of your activities.
So Eddie freakin' squealed.
He didn't. How could an officer
who I put on suspension
say anything at all?
Thanks a lot?
Sorry.
Sorries aren't good enough!
Just what the hell
are we gonna do now?
Survival!
It's basic training.
Lieutenant Randolph
and friends, signing off.
Great.
You're in charge. What now?
We gotta get my father out.
Good morning! And this morning
is our day of new hope.
Our planet,
often beleaguered with
nightmarish social confusion,
has been finally
pieced together again,
with the help from
our true home world.
Federation Chairwoman Everheart
has taken two planets
and given us one
world, one nation.
Today we are reborn
as a unified humanity.
Listen to me, they're going
to blow all of us up!
Straight to hell!
My ALIVEs are not yet
ready to leave.
They're gonna be your tinder
logs in a few seconds.
Papa!
Wilbur, get the important work
into the old storage backups.
Don't worry about me,
I'll be safe.
It's you I'm-
Maybe you are a nut,
but I'm your damn daughter,
and you know it.
This is a police order.
Evacuate.
You're still a little fireball,
aren't you, my Naomi?
Papa!
Armitage!
She's alright. You must think
I'm a great coward, Mr. Sylibus.
But if the ALIVEs
and myself are to die,
I must at least save one thing.
You poor child.
Daddy will fix it.
Daddy will fix his little girl.
There, it's finished,
Naomi. Now you are real.
Last night's slogan of
"one world, one nation"
has this morning blossomed into
a new Martian thought toward
"two worlds, one humanity."
Hey listen, I think Eddie
knows a guy that can hide us
as cargo on an Earth shuttle.
I still got friends there
who can get you a new I.D.
I don't want that.
I'm going back.
Back to St. Lowel.
I don't want to see you die.
You won't have to.
We'll say goodbye here.
That's a good idea, right?
It's a pretty place,
if you just ignore the
smell from all the bombs.
You know I hate when you
talk like shit that way!
So what?
This whole planet
hates your kind,
without any damn reason at all.
Just like I did.
I know they do, but if...
there's someone else.
Oh, Ross, I love
you so very much!
Hey, go wherever you want,
but you're never
gonna lose me now.
Thank you for coming, sir.
This is an MFN
special news break.
Chairwoman Everheart's car
has just turned onto
the main thoroughfare
in downtown St. Lowel.
Her bright smile of success
is met with the cheers
of literally thousands of
admirers lining the streets.
The humanity of Mars
is now whole again.
One world, one nation.
Two thousand.
Look, I'm finished.
It's a little too
angelic for my taste,
but now I've
got some real power.
We'll need it.
Let's show 'em.
A new era in Martian history,
among the brightest
stipulations of the new treaty
is the definition of
the idea of humanity itse-
It's a loading zone only, sir!
You look skinnier.
Is it me, or is it you?
Or no, maybe I'm getting
a lot bigger somehow.
Hmm? What's that?
It's a human I.D. card.
It's the one I promised to you,
before the battle
we had up on Danich Hill.
Ross! Hey, that was
several months ago.
Huh? Who in the hell
is Annalisa Bradford?
Maybe if I had a bunch
of these to begin with,
all the other Thirds could
have gotten away to Earth,
instead of being killed.
You can go wherever
you want with that.
Hey! What are you doing?
Are you nuts? Or just stupid?
I don't know. Maybe both.
I just rather be me now.
Your message mentioned
something about Julian.
Uh, do you wanna go visit him?
No, not yet.
I forgot to tell him
he's gonna be an uncle.
Well, now who's being stupid.
Get it?
The only damage was
in the logic board.
The rest of me was
working just fine.
Ah, what do ya know!
I'm a dad!
You sure are, and I don't wanna
call him Ross Jr. Bradford.