MFN--Martian First Network.
Good evening.
Tonight in headline news
is the continued
terrorist bombings.
Hi, and I am reporting it!
Right.
Just last month,
three bombings occurred.
The last one happened
last night in Well City.
Oh, and wait 'til you hear
how they did it!
Attention to all passengers,
due to a magnetic storm,
all departures are delayed.
We apologize for
any inconvenience.
This has been MAA
information service.
Have a nice day.
Police have determined that
these so-called "puppet bombs"
are the work of
the same terrorist
responsible for
previous explosions.
The pattern was established
after the last incident,
which took place
at Mars airport.
Gee Janet, I hope I won't have
to worry about you blowing up!
Well if I do, I'll
give you an exclusive.
Touché.
I can't believe that I'm
capable of giving birth.
Quite a revelation, isn't it?
That's the whole purpose
of the Third types
You can step beyond the bounds
of conventional robots,
just by getting pregnant,
Mommy Armitage.
Not funny.
It's too weird.
But you, what's your role?
I'm still trying
to figure that out?
What's the point in
creating a male kid?
The CPU showed my serial number
as the last Third made.
The final model off the line.
Not quite.
We can breed now.
Now I understand why the Thirds
were made to seem so human,
not just in appearance,
but emotionally.
Like the murdered singer
and that novelist.
They weren't just machines.
They had souls.
It takes more than the
right plumbing to procreate.
Yes, sir. The perfect
receptacle for human babies.
What the hell
is so funny, huh?
What's the matter?
Have I touched a nerve?
Maternal clock ticking?
Maybe you'd like Detective
Ross to set your alarm.
Shut up.
I was just kidding.
Julian, do you know
why they made us?
I don't.
But I'll bet Asakura does.
Or...D'anclaude.
He must have a part in this.
Christ, another bombing.
That makes 5 this month.
Uh-huh.
So, I guess we'll get stuck
with the investigation.
Uh-huh.
I think it's a pretty crappy
deal if you ask me.
After busting ass
on this Thirds case,
we gotta drop it all
and shift gears.
Uh-huh.
Huh, come in! Chris!
How are you feeling, Ross?
Have you made a full recovery?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just takes some getting
used to the new body parts.
Ironic, isn't it?
What?
Little by little,
you're becoming like the
robots you hate so much.
Let's get down to business,
shall we? Why the new orders?
The bombings don't need
a full-time investigation.
Maybe they do.
Some people would
think it's justified.
It's politics, isn't it?
I'll tell you what it is!
It's a goddamned order
that you're gonna follow!
I don't need to
explain anything to you.
Just do what you're told to!
Am I supposed to smile,
say "Yes, sir," and
forget what they did?
I don't think so.
D'anclaude's under full guard.
Yeah right.
in a government hospital
where we can't touch him.
I can't accept the contradictory
report that you filed.
But, Sir--
I assure you that D'anclaude
is very much alive.
If you don't trust me,
go and see for yourself.
Ironic, isn't it?
Little by little,
you're becoming like the
robots you hate so much.
Do you mean the extortionist?
He's already released.
No, no, René D'anclaude.
Oh yes, the terrorist.
He's still in ICU, I'm afraid.
You can't see him yet.
So what's his condition like?
We have been
sending you updates.
Yes, but I'd like to know more.
Detective,
we've given your department
as much help as we can.
We go through
proper channels here.
That's how
a government-controlled
hospital operates.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have someone waiting for me.
You've got an impressive
security system here.
It's the best form of
protection from terrorists.
Security guards
are old news, pal.
Huh?
Hey, that's Allen.
What's that Conception
PR jerk doing here?
That's where all my memory
was backed up and stored.
I'm saved for posterity.
And if we're all murdered,
you know-
Will you give it a rest!
Bingo!
Warning.
Only authorized personnel
are permitted within
the memory bank I/O room.
Please vacate
this area at once!
We're lost.
Which way is magnetic north?
There is no department
by that name.
You must vacate
within 10 seconds, or-
Asakura was quite a designer.
He created the ultimate
woman who could kick ass
and raise children!
He designed you, too.
Yeah, but I can't get pregnant.
That's it.
Here goes! I hate that
this is the easiest way.
Hey, hurry up!
Hey, I'm doing this for you,
it hurts like Hell, so shut up!
I need to know about myself.
Who am I and why.
I'll look.
I'm searching
for Asakura's file.
Armitage...
Help me out!
My virtual monitor.
Yeah?
Open it from my
navigational system.
Good, I've located
the still image file.
Hold on, just another second.
D'anclaude.
I don't believe it.
Sylibus here.
Where have you been?
The lieutenant's pissed.
Snoopin' for information.
Isn't that what detectives do?
On the old case?
The reception's
breakin' up. Call ya later.
See ya!
Wait! I've got some
hot news for you.
Well, the board from
a puppet bomb that carried
the self-explosion program,
looked identical
to a Third-type board.
Why?
Why is my daddy standing
there with D'anclaude?
Julian!
Damn it! I think
someone's discovered me.
We're logging out now!
Hey!
Oh, god! Something's in me!
Please help me!
Little Naomi Armitage.
Went looking for knowledge
and only found trouble.
You can't stop the Third types
from being killed, my dear.
Shoot me. I don't mind.
Shit! Asshole, get out!
Quite a setup you got here.
With female robots, is this
your "Home Robotization" plan?
Looks like illegal application.
Who the hell do you
think you are?
I don't deal with cop trash--
Well, dickhead, I left my badge
at home, so I'm off duty.
Now you say so.
So tell me, who the
hell's in ICU, huh?
D'anclaude.
Don't fuck with me, asshole!
That crazy bastard's out there.
No! It's really him.
He's Dr. René D'anclaude,
originator of the assassinroid.
No way!
Then it was a robot
who attacked us?
Of course, he's a robot.
His design was based
on character data
of Dr. D'anclaude.
Pull the trigger. I dare you.
So, you're not a man.
Are you a Third type?
Please. You won't find
my name in the membership
of that club for failures.
What do you mean?
You make me retch.
Cheap imitations
pretending to be human.
There's no comparison
to our superiority.
I couldn't agree with
humans more on one thing:
all Thirds should
be annihilated.
I'll kill you!
Julian!
That bastard's
not the original.
Oh my god!
What's wrong?
Don't touch me.
This thing might infect you!
Get back!
Talk, you little shithead.
Tell me about the
assassinroids, now!
Armitage...
Goodbye.
Oh, no, Julian, no!
Sylibus here.
Hello?
Damn thing.
Ross. If you can hear me,
I need your help.
Armitage...
So, one of my men got
a little carried away, well...
I'm Judicial
Vice Minister, Jusup,
and I'm visiting as
a representative of
the Legal Affairs Bureau.
I need an accurate picture
of the MPD's operations.
I'm just a bit confused.
Help me to understand why
an inspector from
Earth's government
has come here.
Oh, don't mind me, Lieutenant.
I'm simply an observer
for Mr. Jusup.
Think of me merely as
a fly on the wall.
Hmm.
Well, since you're observing,
I'm sure you have noticed
that the robots here on Mars
don't quite reflect
a feminist society.
Very well. You understand us,
uh, Mr. uh...
Randolph.
Let's call it
a day and have lunch.
I'm sick of the
whole damn system.
Armitage...
Didn't Julian say that
he had his memory backup
stored somewhere?
The backup?
That's right.
If we can somehow
access his data,
we could still bring him back.
Get it?
His body's gone,
but his mind's alive.
Funny, I didn't think
I would miss him so much.
Maybe his information will help
us and avenge his death as well.
Ross...
come with me.
Looks like the
lieutenant was right.
Humans don't go where
I'm going. Only robots.
Ross.
Where are we?
Whoa.
We're inside the program.
Well, you sure took
your own sweet time.
Julian!
Huh? What?
I'm glad you're here.
Everyone is here.
Other Thirds.
The murdered ones.
So many of us are here,
we don't suffer from loneliness.
A kindred reunion
All of them are my sisters.
It's too bad they lack
the sufficient data,
which would enable them to talk.
I'm sorry. I feel so helpless.
Hey, it's not so bad.
I'm actually having fun.
You can learn a lot in here.
For instance, I've got the
lowdown on D'anclaude now.
Do you mean the original one?
Yes. He and Asakura
developed all the Third types.
Then, do you know
where they are now?
Well, Asakura's files
have been completely erased.
But I know where D'anclaude is.
Shinora?
Right where he's
been all this time.
You should go now.
If you stay too long,
you might not get back.
I'll return. I promise.
K. I'll be waiting.
What's up?
The internal troops are active.
Are we at war?
No. They're guarding.
What, the President?
No, Shinora Hospital.
Shinora?
Jesus H. Christ, would
you look at that arsenal!
What the hell are
they doin' there?
Hold on a minute.
I'm picking up something.
What is it?
Aw, it's just a car.
Holy shit!
They've lost it.
Fire!
Here.
It's him.
Finally, the real D'anclaude.
Or I should say
Dr. René D'anclaude.
You must be...
Asakura's daughter,
the failure.
We gotta hurry! Come on!
Let's go, while we still can.
What's the matter?
Ross,
something's coming.
What is it?
Not again.
D'anclaude! But it can't be.
Hey, let's rumba!
Over here!
This way, hurry!
Wait, don't run off!
I wanna play with you.
Come on! Wait!
There's no way that damn
gargoyle is a Third type!
Hmm. My, look who's talking.
Don't tell me you have no
clue who your brother was.
You have more in common
with that prototype gargoyle
than you might realize.
Did you truly believe
you were a Third?
Liar!
You could always ask Asakura,
but he's tucked safely away
in a dome on Danich Hill.
Armitage, don't stop.
No!
Oh no, I can always tell when
you're gonna do something crazy.
Hi kids.
Oh, does she want a showdown?
We're both gonna bite it.
That'll make everyone happy,
cause you know, nobody
on Mars wants us here.
Wrong! I'll have the last laugh.
Don't!
No, Armitage!
We can no longer
return to the city.
First, they denied us life. Then
they tried to erase our past.
But I'm not going to run.
I'm staying right here.
Armitage III, episode 4,
"Bit of Love."
Ross, we're not gonna
die this time, are we?