Attention ladies and gentlemen,
we are now on final approach
to our destination port
of St. Lowel,
the largest city on Mars.
We hope you had
a pleasant flight.
Today's temperature is a
cool eleven degrees Celsius.
The oxygen percentage
rating is seven percent.
Reports have come in of slight
unrest throughout the city
due to public demonstrations.
As a precaution,
we recommend using
the airport shuttle
service for your safety.
We hope you have an enjoyable
time during your stay on Mars.
Aw, c'mon Kelly.
Babe, we've got
a schedule to keep.
You can't break the rules
like you did on Earth.
I'm sick and tired of working,
and I just want
some time on my own.
Why are you being so selfish?
I hope my guitar's alright.
Well, we paid enough.
Cargo room costs bucks.
Don't worry, Babe.
Your guitar is treated
like a national treasure.
Please remain seated and
keep your seatbelts fastened
until we've come to a full stop.
We wish to thank our passengers
for their patronage,
and we look forward to
servicing you in the future.
Have a nice day.
Hmm?
It's the cargo room.
Huh?
I'm sure McCanon would
love to give an autograph!
Home on the range.
Hey, watch out!
Freeze, get your hands up!
I said, "Get your
hands up!" Now!
What's up?
Detective, you'd
better stay back.
Handle it.
Get back!
Tell me you're
packin' a gun, Sheriff.
How 'bout you?
Shit. Cowboys out the ass,
and not one of 'em's got a gun.
Stop, now!
Lemme down! Lemme down!
Look, the bastard's
getting away!
What the hell?
Stay out of it, Detective.
This is the MPD,
Detective Sylibus.
Did you have a nice trip?
There's a body in there! Oh no!
It's McCanon
He killed her!
Haha!
Dammit.
Hey, wait! What the
hell are ya doin'?
Stop!
This is insane.
Her name was Kelly McCanon,
famous country singer.
In fact, the only country singer
in the universe.
I guess this means
they're extinct.
And the suspect?
Tell me, is that
crazy getup you're wearing
standard issue MPD uniform?
Of course not.
What's your name?
The name's Armitage.
Ooh, what a sexy back.
I just love broad shoulders.
Huh?
What's that for?
I was just being nice!
Hey, is this somebody's
idea of a sick joke?
Annie Oakley here
isn't even human.
It's a damn robot.
What's wrong?
What's goin' on?
Airport police.
This is their jurisdiction.
Look, they're here.
Great, now we get some answers.
Over here!
Sir, sir, are you with the MPD?
I'm with Mars Broadcasting.
We've heard rumor that
the murdered Kelly McCanon
was actually a robot.
Uh, is this true? There
are conflicting reports.
Can you shed any
light on this at all?
No comment.
I'm reporting from the front of
the Martian Police Department.
An officer from the
scene where country singer
Kelly McCanon's body
was discovered is here now.
He has not, however,
given any information,
and only replies "No
comment," to our questions.
Back to you.
The million dollar question is,
"What do we have here,
a woman or a robot?"
The results from my preliminary
findings are, well, uh...
ambivalent.
The, uh, victim,
shall we call her,
is neither human nor cyborg.
After initially
examining the body,
I concluded she was a robot.
Her body tissue was
clearly of organic origin,
but she functioned through
artificial intelligence.
While no one is capable of
creating a human brain, yet,
her computer brain
was very sophisticated,
and as I mentioned,
her physical construction
was created organically,
but it was done using
a technology much more advanced
than the second series models.
I believe the victim
was a prototype,
built outside of regulations.
It could also, um, mean there
are other illegal models,
like her,
running around under our noses.
Yes, thank you.
Now Detective Sylibus will give
us his report about the scene.
Uh, I'm Officer Ross Sylibus,
from Chicago.
The suspect appeared, I mean,
he seemed like he wanted
to transport the body
without anyone noticing.
Hmm, probably to finish his
work somewhere else in private.
Officer Armitage, there,
had been trailing the suspects,
and all hell broke loose.
Armitage, can you fill us in.
Well, I trailed the suspects
and saw they were equipped.
I didn't think they were
carrying a dead robot.
So what the hell does that mean?
That it was McCanon's
imposter riding the shuttle?
Shut up, Eddie.
What did her manager
have to say?
Well, sir, according
to him, he didn't see
any difference between
the woman he sat with and
the real country-western singer.
And nobody saw her come out
of the arriving terminal.
The only suspicious passenger
he saw was Detective Sylibus.
Well, it seems that the real
trick for us is to find out
where the real McCanon is.
You know, maybe she's
feeling her wild oats.
Might've found herself
some kinda wild lover.
Christ, Eddie, will you zip it?
How was she acting
inside the shuttle?
She acted fine. She was
holding a normal conversation,
nothing seemed unusual
about it to me.
Hell, I wouldn'ta been able
to tell her apart from a human.
Uh-huh. Uh...
Are you tellin' us that this
robot was really McCanon?
You think that prima donna was
a machine from the beginning?
No, I'm saying you can't
distinguish it from a human.
Oh, hey Armitage,
when you realized the corpse
was a robot, you were shocked,
even upset.
Did you think something
was wrong? Well, did ya?
No, sir.
Whoa.
The sky is beautiful.
Fourth floor.
Hmm.
Eew, smells stale. Hey,
is that all your luggage?
Well, you know,
with all the excitement
at the baggage claim today...
Just as well, probably stuff
I wouldn't have needed anyway.
There's enough trash
from Earth here already.
Hmm, you do have a point.
Oh, look at this.
This is a tape, sent by
the suspect of yesterday's
St. Lowel spaceport shooting.
♪ Here where we belong. ♪
What is this? Some kind
of memorial program?
♪ We belong... ♪
The following scenes
contain graphic content,
and viewer discretion
is advised.
If you have children,
please set your monitor to "L".
That's the guy!
I'll go take care
of the baggage maid.
Who are you?
Uh!
Uh, somebody, please help me.
Please, stop. Tell me,
why are you doing this?
Uh!
My god!
Jessica!
And there it is. In all
of its brutal detail.
We have with us,
in the studio today,
famous activist for
the Neo-humanist cause,
Julia Blanshin,
who will offer commentary
on this extraordinary footage.
Welcome, Miss Blanshin.
Contrary to what your
viewers might be expecting,
I'm not here to condemn the
actions of the man we just saw.
Our goal is to eliminate
all robots from every level
of industry and society
and reclaim our humanity.
The same goal as
the suspect may have had?
Well, perhaps, but we
don't believe the problem
can be solved by
street-level violence.
We advocate
proper social changes.
Jennifer!
Hold on! You'll be alright.
You pile of shit!
Come on, you fucker!
Come on! Come on!
Amazing, they're
everywhere ya look.
You'd think they
could build something else.
You're here pretty early,
Detective.
Hmm?
She's gone already,
the badge-toting
terror in hot-pants.
Hey, want some free advice?
Don't kill your
partner this time.
Here's one more thing, when she
puts on her visor, watch out.
Oh, before I forget, here.
She's clean, gassed,
and waitin' downstairs.
And welcome to your new home.
Check it out, it's a Ferrari!
Oh wow, this is too cool!
Hey, has it got
four on the floor?
Nope, it's a fully
guided automatic.
But I drive it myself.
Whoa.
Hey.
Actually, I don't
trust machines.
Listen to that sweet engine.
You know something,
the lieutenant just
bought a new car.
It's a stick-shift.
Before he got rid of the
old car, he realized that
he'd never driven it
by himself before.
I tried to stop him, well,
before he took it out,
cause you know, it's dangerous,
don't you think?
I mean, a person
that never dro-
Robots, get out!
Get out right now!
Give us back our jobs!
I'm sorry to
break you in so soon,
but we may as well get started.
Ah, but Lieutenant,
is our section supposed
to handle this matter?
Hmm?
What do you mean by that, Ross?
Well, you see, the victim
was definitely a robot,
so I don't see why MPD should
get stuck dealing with it.
Shouldn't we let some government
agency take it off our hands?
I wish it was that easy,
but it's the robot's origins
that we're interested
in finding out about.
As you may not be aware,
Sylibus, people here consider
illegal robotic technology
and replication to be
a criminal offense!
Yes, sir, I guess so.
Are you going to tell me why
you wanted to transfer to Mars?
Well, no sir.
As you like,
but let me warn you,
if you have misguided
compassion for robots,
you won't make it here.
Robots, get out!
Get out right now!
Huh?
Hi!
Hmm, coulda sworn it was
winter outside. That's weird.
Have you been
watchin' the news?
This is a photo of the corpse.
It's being called
a third-series robot.
Know anything about it?
Ah, I see you've
done your research.
Yes, she was
a clever little model,
certainly not mass-produced.
No, it's my guess
she was handmade.
Does your company manufacture
any robots like this?
This is not the type of
robot Hu-Gite manufactures.
That's how we surpassed
the Conception company
and became the best.
We're very proud
of our philosophy,
are you familiar with it?
Ah.
Home Robotization. Making
the robot a part of the family
by making it more functional.
A humanoid robot
simply doesn't work.
There has to be a reason and
purpose for a robot's existence.
When they've achieved that,
humans and robots
will live in harmony,
and that's the belief upon
which our company is founded.
Have you noticed how
many different brands
there are running
around here on Mars?
When Mars terraforming began,
history shows
that robots were used
for environmental
testing and labor.
Well, I'm amazed
we've come this far.
Me, too.
In spite of our progress,
people are afraid.
They misunderstand
the potential of robots.
Our hope, our dream,
isn't shared by everyone yet.
Do you hear us?
We want our jobs!
We want our-
Wow, what a place.
Uh, excuse me, Miss.
Why not!?
I'm very sorry,
but I've explained to you
that I cannot
allow you to see him!
He doesn't remember
the name Armitage at all?!
Mr. Asakura said
he's never heard of you.
Listen, don't mess with me,
you little bitch.
You'd better get out of here,
or I'll call
the security gadget.
Yeah, I guess it's useless
talking to a robot like you.
Hey, whoa!
Uh, just cancel
that appointment.
Robots, get out!
Let me go!
How dare you?
I have business here.
Stop it!
I can't believe this!
Put me down right now!
We want our jobs back!
Just what are you trying
to accomplish back in there?
Robots get out now!
You know if you park here,
your car might get trashed.
Yeah!
Idiots.
So, now what's next?
Hmm, immigration
seems a likely place.
Oh Ross, I already went there,
and I couldn't find
our guy on the list.
Hmm.
Oh, I doubt we'll
find any record of him,
because 37% of the population
isn't registered here.
So, just who the hell
were you trying to see
at the Conception company?
That is private.
By the way, I've already
done some legwork.
Conception was the company
that set the standards
for the Seconds,
so there you go.
But you know,
I still pity them.
The other manufacturer,
Hu-Gite, passed 'em up,
and it killed their aspirations.
Say, does this fancy machine
have reclining seats?
Partner?
If you're looking for
a partner, stop flying solo.
Hey, Ross, as your partner,
can I make a suggestion?
What?
Let's eat. I'm starving.
All right.
Ice cream.
Junk food?
I thought we were gonna
get something to eat?
Oh well, whatever.
This is some town.
Things are just
gonna get worse
with all these
remodeled Seconds.
There's no way humans and robots
are gonna get along together.
Besides, you can't trust robots.
You're no different.
You and that guy
are both the same.
What do you mean,
that nutcase?
It just seems that both of you
have something against robots.
I'm sick of all these cyborgs
and humanoids and machines
that only seem to copy us.
Since I'm allowed
to make a choice,
I choose not to like something
that pretends to be human.
Uh!
Hmm?
Hmph.
You're investigating
her identity.
Is that right, Detective?
Yes, it's my job.
I wonder... Kelly's fans,
what they must be thinking now.
She was the most
human girl I knew.
She was so sensitive
and in touch.
She didn't listen
to her manager, though.
Nope, cause she
always did things her way.
Tell me, how could
she be a robot? Hah!
It's too funny, isn't it?
I don't believe it.
She was a real woman.
I know what you
must be going through,
but did you recall
anything unusual or
out of the ordinary with her?
Excuse me.
Please, tell me
she's still alive.
Won't you, huh, huh?
Come on, no robot can make a
guitar weep the way Kelly did.
You understand, don't you?
Or sing with the same passion...
Armitage!
Your client is history, buddy.
Just learn to live with it.
Hey!
Hey, wait up! Armitage!
I want to go!
Your conduct was
hardly professional.
Sorry, but that
whiner was an asshole.
Maybe you sympathize
with him, but I don't.
The jerk can't figure out how
a robot could possibly be as
good as his precious human star.
All of McCanon's
talents, personality,
and dreams were
inside that machine.
Oh my god.
What is it?
I didn't realize.
Sylibus here.
Uh, it's Chris.
I'm receiving a weird
voicemail transmission.
Is Armitage with you?
Uh, no. I'm afraid
I don't see her right now.
Okay, listen. It's coming
to us in real time.
So I'll transmit it
to your mailbox.
Log it and show it
to Armitage right away.
I told you! An officer
named Armitage!
Okay, okay, lady. We're
looking for her right now.
Please! You've got to help me!
I'm a Third!
Right, what's your name again?
Wait a second,
alright, go ahead.
Manning. It's Jessica Manning.
I'm keeping a list of all
the Thirds from Pluto.
We need protection.
I can't go outside,
because of the protests.
And the man on TV
who killed that singer
has been sending me mail!
I know he's nearby.
I know he's watching me!
Something's gonna happen,
unless you help me!
Who are you?
Bye, see you tomorrow!
TV piracy is a felony, pal.
You could get eight years
of hard labor in prison.
Who the hell are you?
I'm René D'anclaude.
Huh?
It's my name.
So just who do you
think you are, mister?
There are other things to
concern yourselves with.
Let me show you.
Robots are disguising
themselves as humans.
Am I wrong?
It's my duty
to do something about this.
You must be rid of those
so-called Thirds.
First contestant:
This is Jessica Manning,
Shit.
a snobbish, bourgeois artist
who lives and works
right here among you.
She had you all fooled.
What should we do about her?
Are you okay, miss,
or you need help?
Jessica! Save her please! Why?
It's all right, just wait here.
Lemme through. Police!
Hey!
Huh?
It's them. The list of Thirds.
Yes. And then?
No, wait!
Oh, Jessica.
Huh?
Who-hooooo!
Stop!
Upsy daisy!
If you've come to confess your
sins, it's too late, my son.
There's no room for
religion on Mars anymore.
If you like,
I'll listen to you.
What's that?
You say a cyborg
killed your partner?
Then you should join me.
You know, the more
human a robot looks,
the more excitement I feel
killing the damn thing.
I wish you'd reconsider, Ross.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
Aww.
I'm just exterminating
vermin, a pestilence.
I'm performing a service.
Why am I made out to be
the bad guy, Ross?
Maybe you and I can sit down
over coffee and talk about it.
Oh shit, not again.
Ross, Ross, you're such
a pesky little shit.
Now then, there are lots
of Thirds I have to destroy.
I just can't
have you underfoot.
Hey, sailor. What's this?
You've gotta be kidding!
A fake leg?
Surely the ironic humor
of this hasn't escaped you.
You're almost a stinking
cyborg yourself, you freak.
What's that?
Huh?
It's Armitage.
A bell to mourn the dead.
Don't you think you should
tell your friend there
isn't a god on Mars anymore?
D'anclaude, let me tell you why
your crimes won't be forgiven.
Why am I here to avenge the
murders of innocent robots?
How can I justify the
existence of the Third?
I'll tell you!
It's in my blood.
It's my destiny.
She's nuts.
Now you'll learn.
The truth is, René,
I'm also a Third.
No you're not.
That's your last mistake.
How can you be a Third?
Your name wasn't
even on my list.
Don't let the name fool you.
I'm hardly third rate.
Let me show you!
Here, bitch!
You like it hot?
You monster.
Huh.
Yeah, that's right,
I'm a monster.
I'm the monster society created.
I'm the thing they blame for
recession and social problems.
I'm the scapegoat!
If humans don't want me,
why did they make me?
Don't do it!
Just cuff him.
You're a police
officer first, Armitage.
You know what your duty is.
Robots aren't the
enemy of humans.
I learned this from my partner.
No, don't look at me.
I don't know what
I'm supposed to be.
I feel like some
kind of hideous puppet.
I can walk and talk. And I
can... laugh and I- I can cry.
But I'm still just a doll.
Armitage!
No!
C'mon, kid.
Don't short out on me.
C'mon! C'mon! Get up! Get up!
Hey, Armitage.
Come on, kid,
open up your eyes.
You've gotta wake up now.
Oh thank God.
Thank God? For what?
God is human. God made me
in his image. Ha, right!
Do you know what
it's like to be me?
You couldn't possibly
imagine what it's like.
Hey, where you goin'?
Goodbye, Ross.
My name is Armitage,
and I am a Third.
Feelings? Yes I have them.
Memories, too.
But where are the other Thirds?
I've got to find them!
Armitage III, Episode 2,
"Flesh &amp; Stone."
Ross, don't follow me.