Damn it.
You bastard.
Don't take my life.
Please don't hurt me.
I'm not the only one. Please.
Why did you pick me?
No, don't-
Aw, shit.
Oh my god!
The corpse was identified
as Lavinia Whately, age 24.
She worked as a dancer.
And she's also a Third.
How many robots are there?
Seems you can't swing a
dead cat without hitting one.
Detective Sylibus.
Mars to Sylibus, come in.
Uh, what?
Are you conscious enough
to report on a doll
killer René D'anclaude.
Yes. He's at a
hospital in Shinora.
He was admitted to ICU, where
his condition is still critical.
He's no better than
a vegetable,
but to cover our butts,
he has round-the-clock security.
The police hospital, huh?
Could he have an accomplice?
Well, we can't question him.
She really worked him over good.
You really made her day, huh?
Christ, Eddie, will
you put a lid on it?
I just wonder
where she's gone to.
Why have all the Thirds
so far been female?
Lowel...
do you have any
new information?
You monster.
Yeah, that's right,
I'm a monster.
I'm the monster society created.
I'm the thing they blame for
recession and social problems.
I'm the scapegoat!
If humans don't want me,
why did they make me?
The first five humanoid cadavers
were illegally manufactured.
Our labs were not
equipped to examine them.
Therefore they've been sent to
a facility at the Conception
Company to be analyzed.
Since they're the
experts in this field,
we're hoping they can give us
a clue to the Thirds' origins.
But--
But they haven't turned up
any preliminary findings yet?
No, they claim
it's inconclusive
Oh, I think you had better
examine the sixth one yourself.
Yes, sir.
Uh, Sylibus, I have something
I want to talk to you about,
so come to my office later.
Yes.
Armitage carries
a Special A Class license.
I know.
But she chose to
become a cop. A good one.
Do you understand
I'm getting at?
Yeah.
If the reason she disappeared
is because of you, Ross.
Well, you can
interrogate me all you want.
I'm used to it.
Ross, that won't be necessary.
If you say you
don't know anything,
that's good enough for me.
Leave it at that.
I'm no Sherlock Holmes,
but I've learned from experience
to follow my instinct.
I have a hunch there's some kind
of connection between Armitage
and the killing
of the Third types.
This could get real fun.
If an officer was
rumored to be a humanoid,
the shit could hit the fan.
So let's keep this between
you, me, and the wall.
Armitage isn't a good cop.
She's a great one.
Always hurts like hell
when the rain comes.
Start message.
Hey, where are you?
You okay? Your
partner's concerned.
The lieutenant's no dummy.
He suspects you're a Third.
It appears D'anclaude
is working with someone,
because Thirds are
still being murdered.
Don't let bitterness change you.
Come back, Armitage. Please.
It appears D'anclaude
is working with someone,
because Thirds are
still being murdered.
Don't let bitterness change you.
Come back, Armitage. Please.
Good evening, Mademoiselle.
A bit late for such a lovely
wench to be out strolling.
Say, maybe you
could spare ten credits
so a poor soul could
get a beer from Earth?
Now behave. Alright?
Perhaps you gents know
someone who lives near here,
a novelist.
A writer. I myself used to be
a fine writer of on-line porno.
You could say I was
on the cutting edge.
Let's see what you got
in here, Baby.
Get away from me!
What's the hurry, Sport?
Thought you wanted to play.
I'm sorry!
Good.
You don't know how sorry I am.
I just love a man who grovels.
Now then, you will
answer my questions.
I will! Everything, just ask!
Oh, that feels nice.
You're crazy!
Your turn.
You're a monster!
You've got an appointment set
up at the Conception Company.
Ask for Mr. Allen.
He's in charge.
O.K. I'll get
on my way right now.
Oh, yeah. Check this out!
I came across a log of
correspondence Armitage
did just before she vamoosed.
What are you
talkin' about, Eddie?
Voila.
Correspondence with who?
I can't tell you yet.
It's in machine language.
I'll have to try reverse
computations first.
It's in code?
My boy, leave everything
up to old Eddie.
I'll decipher it.
You can count on me.
Uh, yeah.
Are you Detective
Sylibus from the MPD?
Thanks for fitting me in today.
I'm Eugene Allen,
Vice President of
public relations.
Please, won't you sit down?
Thanks.
I'm here to discuss
the examination reports
on the Thirds we've
requested from your company.
Uh, yes, we're working on it.
The architecture of
that particular type
is very different
from our designs,
so it's taking some time.
Unforeseen delays.
Even so, we need to...
Uh, is your AL product,
the Artificial Life androids,
those composed of
organic fibers,
a high demand
commodity for you?
Yes, very.
What purpose do we serve
by simulating humans?
Are you familiar with
our motto, Detective?
Yeah, "Home Robotization."
A rather hot political,
legal topic at the moment.
I realize you're trying to pass
new standards to get your cut
of the market.
It's only natural to want
to make a profit, right?
It sounds like you're implying
that we're manufacturing Thirds.
An observation.
Let's see, um,
there was somethin' else.
Asakura was an inventor
who worked on your staff.
Asakura? Well,
I'm afraid he's not here.
Not here? What do
you mean he's not here?
He quit.
When?
He quit before
I joined the company,
several years ago.
Hmm, I understand.
You're welcome to
check employee files.
Everything can be verified.
So, is she an example
of "Home Robotization"?
Well, one purpose of robots
is to help turn human
fantasies into reality.
They can do almost
anything, can't they?
Except reproduce.
Please, visit us again sometime.
Drive home safely, and be
sure to have a nice day. Bye!
Sorry to take up your time.
It's no problem.
Please drive safely, and be
sure to wear your seatbelt.
Human fantasy!
She sounds like my mother.
Give me personnel code copy.
Please enter
authorized user password.
Thank you.
Access Third type, wild search.
No subject data located.
Access Asakura, wild search.
Subject data locked.
Shut down.
I know Conception
is hiding something.
This makes number seven.
I think I'm gonna puke.
Who the hell's doing this?
I can only think of two people
with the means and motivation.
I'm talking about
René D'anclaude and Armitage.
What's that?
Yeah, I know it's
weird to think about,
but she talked to
me about it once.
She pities the robots
used for crime,
so she kills them quickly.
But I can't believe
she'd actually...
Not on your life.
I'm sure the village is artsy,
but downtown is a pit.
I wouldn't move there
for anything.
Listen, I've gotta
get some writing done.
I'll talk to ya later.
Continue writing mode.
Novel in progress, untitled.
Chapter 2, paragraph 5.
"How could she greet the
ones from the deep far away?
"She, who has spent a pleasant
and enchanting afternoon...
"who had never given a
thought about the person
from the Luluie,
the same one who had once picked
her up, now cold and dead."
"A phantom."
"Her battle with
the old gods ended.
"As a spiritual truce
was struck,
she felt her soul unburdened.
"She smiled. Already the
feeling of harmony was-"
Who's there?
Who are you?
Are you Armitage?
Are you the one
who contacted me?
You fooled me!
You fooled me.
You fooled me...
Do you mean Armitage
is a suspect?
Well, you can't
just deny the evidence.
The woman's last
words said it all.
The whole department is shocked,
but the lieutenant had
suspicions about her all along.
He's already issued a
warrant for her arrest.
And there's
an APB out on her.
That sly old dog.
Access mail.
Log file, Armitage.
Open file.
This is Pluto.
I'm sending this message
by using Armitage's ID.
I'm a Third, just like you...
Hey, Chris. Let's find out
where this mail originated from
You got it.
Shit.
Ha! That's it. That's it.
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon.
Jackpot!
Here is the complete list
of Thirds from Pluto.
Pluto? The planet?
Huh, whoa, so that's
the game. Hot damn.
Lieutenant, come here, quick!
Just hold on. Are you certain?
Yes, sir.
Although to get the results,
I did have to send a piece
of the body to the
Conception Company.
But how? Technically,
can they really...
Why not? They're physically
equipped the same as humans are.
I wasn't talking about that!
Get me Ross!
Yes, sir!
It's Sylibus.
Is it true you put a warrant
out for Armitage's arrest?
I had no choice, but Eddie
figured out the pattern.
As we expected,
it's a list of Thirds.
I'll bet Pluto
ends that list, right?
How did you know?
I made an illegal search
and found a message.
Uh, that's just between
you, me, and the wall.
I'll call you later.
There's one more thing.
We finally learned why
all the Thirds are female.
What?
Lavinia Whately was pregnant.
Pregnant?
Androids that can reproduce?
That must be the
purpose of the Thirds.
Hey Kelly, wanna see
a movie Saturday?
Hey guys!
Look!
Whoa.
Geez, what's with
all the weird getup?
Wonder what the heck
she's doing here.
Wow.
Morning Mrs. Brewster.
Good morning.
Now everyone get inside.
Hurry up.
Class will start
in a few minutes.
Armitage.
I used to love the
playground after school.
I was a pretty
clumsy kid, though.
I took a tumble off
the see-saw once and
bawled all the way home.
Listen, did you know that the
MPD has been searching for you?
Bet you're looking
for Pluto, right?
Let's go.
Armitage!
What?
Armitage, I just wanted to...
You and... uh... nevermind.
There! That's him,
I'm sure of it.
Huh? But, he's a boy.
How do you do, Pluto?
It's good to meet you.
There's no need
for such formality.
We are brother and sister.
You've forgotten.
I'm sorry.
By the way, shouldn't
you be in class?
No, I'm transferring
my thoughts
to the main memory at
the navigation center.
Hmm?
What for?
To make a backup
of myself, obviously.
I appreciate you
sending the list, Pluto.
Please don't call me
by my handle.
It's embarrassing.
Very well, Julian Moore.
I never imagined
a child Third...
and a boy to boot.
The most sophisticated AL model,
but I'm incapable of maturing.
I'm trapped in this body.
Until I'm destroyed
Do you know that for sure?
I heard that I have
the distinction of being
the last model off
the Thirds test line.
So they made me a child,
and a male no less.
The joke's on me, isn't it?
I don't get it.
Later.
She doesn't catch on too
quick. There's no need for her
to be concerned
with it now anyway.
Why, you!
Even though you're a Third
for all intents and purposes,
you're a punk.
Talk to me again like that,
and I'll paddle your cyborg ass!
What's wrong?
Why'd the elevator stop?
I don't know.
Huh?
It won't stop!
We're dropping pretty fast.
At this rate,
we're gonna die for sure.
Hold on tight to him!
Do you really think
this is gonna work?
Got any ideas?
Ross.
I think my right arm
and some ribs are broken.
Time to meet our assassin.
Damn you!
He's fast.
Come on, we gotta run for it.
Go on. Leave me here.
No, I'll help you. Let's go!
Oh, my god.
Looks like a showdown.
Aim it up!
If Armitage is killed, then
there's gonna be no hope for me.
D'anclaude!
Who's in Shinora, then?
Surprise, surprise!
Didja miss me?
You son of a bitch!
I won't let you
die alone, cherie.
The other two will join you.
Fucking bastard!
He's not human!
Nice right hook,
but now I'm going to crush
the three of you,
and get on with my life.
I have places to go,
and people to kill!
Huh?
Huh? What the-
Hi there, René. Bon voyage.
You crazy bitch!
Give me the key!
Please, unlock it!
Bye!
A burial in the sewer.
Poetic justice.
I knew you weren't the killer.
No one suspected it might be
that psycho again.
Security should be
here any minute.
They'll take care of you.
No.
You don't have
to run and hide.
Police don't leave
their injured behind.
You're cold, lady.
I will always be cold.
Armitage.
Old questions unanswered.
New ones arise.
Why are Thirds
being slaughtered?
For what purpose
are they intended?
Why are they
designed to reproduce?
Where is Asakura?
And is it really René D'anclaude
at the hospital in Shinora?
I have no choice but to go.
Armitage III, Episode 3,
"Heart Core."