Who is the king? It's you!
Okay! Looks like it's me!
Let's see here.
I want everyone to worship me
and tell me I'm beautiful!
'Cause I'm king.
Obey me or die!
Of course, we will obey,
your majesty.
Asuka, I think you're taking
this "king" idea too far.
Just give us your orders.
I'm pretty sure worshipping
her was her order.
"Oh, king you're so beautiful,
I'll worship you forever."
I'm bored with this,
who goes next, huh?
Hey, no fair, don't try
to cheat me out of my turn!
I'm still the king!
I guess I can't let
my guard down at all, can I?
Usurper!
Alright, let's think here.
Number One, you have
to rub Number Three's breasts.
Wait!
Hold on a second.
That's a little stereotypical,
don't you think?
Yes, I completely agree.
It just seems ridiculous.
I really don't want
to do that, Asuka.
It's creepy.
Do it.
Wow!
They're so big!
Hey, are you on some kinda
special diet or something?
Incredible!
My hands won't stop moving!
Not so rough, please!
This is just
starting to piss me off.
We're all girls, so why
is there such a difference
in our chest size?
I'm not sure
I'm cool with this!
This is like sex education.
Okay, I'm pulling
the next straw.
Jiggle-jiggle, Jiggle-jiggle,
Jiggle-jiggle, Jiggle-jiggle.
Oh, no!
Hey, everybody, it's your
favorite jockey of the disc.
But what's this?
I've been dissed.
Nobody invited me
to the singles party.
This is DJ Condor's
'Love Letters From the Abyss!'
That's right, I'm the host
with the most, but tonight
I can't boast,
because as a matter of fact,
I have never been
invited to a singles party.
I'm DJ Condor,
the singles party virgin.
But who knows, maybe tonight's
the night I'll get that invite
and pop that party cherry?!
I can't take this anymore!
Hey, what's up?
You showed up again, huh?
Thanks, that makes me happy.
If everyone else in this crazy
world was as nice as you,
maybe life here would be
a little more tolerable.
But, what can you do?
Life sucks and then you die.
This is why some people
fall to their knees and pray.
While others are content to
just get on with their lives.
Oh, come on, are you kidding me?
That's just a show he puts on.
No, he's a real cutie,
that one.
Yeah, but I hear he can have
a real mean streak sometimes;
that's what worries me.
No way!
Trust me on this one;
he's all bark and no bite.
Well, I do want him to be sweet.
But also to be tough enough
that he makes me feel safe.
What, is she buyin' a dog?
Woof!
Don't forget: whenever he yells
'I'll friggin' kill you!',
it's his way of
showing he cares.
Huh?
Are you talkin' about me?!
Drac, where'd you come from?
I just got here.
Five seconds ago.
Why don't you stop with
the gossip and do your job?
Well.
This girl's a customer.
Then how 'bout you shut
your yap and make her a crepe.
No, this girl's your customer.
Huh?
Hey, look.
This is the fixer guy
I was telling you about.
The Narita Contractor's Office.
Who told her about me?
I bet she doesn't
even have any money.
So, what do you want?
Oh, well.
It's really no big deal.
I mean, it's not like
it's life or death,
It's not important at all.
Oh, yeah?
Well then,
why don't you just go home?
Huh?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I'd better go.
So sorry to bother you.
Don't be so scared.
He's just an asshole, okay?
It's not like he's mad at you
or anything like that.
That's just the way he is.
Really?
I thought he hated me.
Just shut up.
See?
It's just like I said.
He's so cute when
he gets all worked up.
Did I just see you blush?
Listen up, wench, who do you
think you're dealin' with, huh?
The question is: who do you
think you're dealing with?
Hey, I've got a rep to keep up,
and if you don't cut it out
right now, I'm gonna smack
you six ways from Sunday,
you harlot!
I love it when he gets
all feisty like this.
It's adorable, isn't it?
Look, Drac.
You're a businessman,
aren't you?
Well, you've got a customer
standing right in front of you.
Thank you for your business.
I am your friendly,
neighborhood fixer,
from the
Narita Contractor's Office.
Oh, why, thank you.
All right.
What can I do for you?
Oh, I, Uh. Well, you see.
Thing is-
Uh, never mind, I'm good.
So, you don't need my help?
I guess I've only judged her
by her face, huh?
But now that
I really look at her,
she kind of reminds
me of Shusuke.
Enough already,
the girl's looking for a bike.
Huh?
A bike?
Yes, sir, it's a 'two-wheeler,'
as we used to call it back home.
She set it down here,
and took her eyes off of it
for just a second, and then
somebody ran off with it.
Drac, help her find it.
Oh, don't be ridiculous,
that thing's gone for good.
If you steal a bike, you'd be
stupid not to get rid of it
as quickly as possible,
there's no way we're
ever gonna find that--
Quit your grumbling and do
something about it, you jerk!
You're so negative!
I'm tryin' to be realistic--
Are you gonna do it or not?
Make up your mind!
Quit smackin' me in the head,
you succubus,
you're gonna give me
split-ends or somethin'.
Oh please, what do you care?
I doubt you even
wash your hair.
The hell I don't!
I washed it just this morning,
for your information!
With conditioner
and everything!
She can laugh
just like a normal kid.
I get what you're
sayin' about the bike.
You see that?
Told you he'd help you out.
No, it's just, I forgot to
ask you somethin' important.
How did you even hear about me?
Ka- Uh, I mean, from one
of my brother's friends.
What's his name?
A big guy named 'Mister Soda'.
His right and left hand
were like, 'yo, yo.'
So are you with the YFB.
Or-?
No, not me, But you
might have heard of
my big brother actually,
he's the top guy
in the organization.
Wait, is your last name Otori?
Well, yes!
My name is Naru Otori.
Naru Otori.
It's my first time to meet her,
But I definitely know
who her brother is.
A year ago, I had a run-in
with the city's so called,
'watch group.' The
Yanagihara Flame Birdes,
but truth be told,
they're really just
a bunch of useless punks.
That was the first time
I ran into Kakeru Otori.
The de facto leader of the YFB.
The imperial majesty
of crazy nights.
Long time since
I've met a fellow freak.
Let's dance!
Naïve, yes?
Mistaken, yes?
I'm dead wrong, yes?!
Reveal yourself
to me, you punk!
Well, well, you're worthy.
Come, join the Flame Birdes
and soar with us.
You can be one of the chosen.
Don't stray, no matter what!
Excuse me, but would you mind
if I asked you something?
Oh, yeah.
Sure, go for it.
Why is it that everybody
around here calls you, Drac?
Well.
You see, the only time I
ever show up around here
is at night, So I got
called 'Dracula.'
Oh.
Well, I guess that makes sense.
He loves that name; make sure
to use it as much as you can.
Oh?
You're sure that's okay?
Just shut up!
You do know you're
not her boss, right?
So quit orderin' her around
and let her do what she wants.
Yeah, and what if I don't stop?
You're not gonna do anything
about it but stand there
and look pissed.
That's all you do!
Well fine.
What else can you do
at times like this?
That the world may know peace.
Pardon me?
Thank you for helping
me out, Mr. Drac.
Thank you so much.
Uh, Yeah.
All righty then!
Manuscript received.
Huh?!
Wait, you already read it?
How is that even possible?
Is it really that bad?
Oh, no.
You've got it all wrong,
I believe in you, kid.
Okay--I'm not sure
how to take that, but-
I could really use
some more work,
so if there's anything
you need, just let me know.
As a matter of fact, I happen to
have a job for you right here.
I need a review on this book
that was just released.
And I need it by next month.
Huh, "Youth Cannot Resist It",
by Tama Izumi.
So what is it about?
It's a new work from
our publishing company.
An autobiographical piece
by an ex-porno starlet.
I need you to gush all over it
like you always do, okay?
One fluff piece coming right up!
Our readers are really
starting to like your column.
Meet your deadline
and keep up the good work.
Try not to be like Kakeru.
That idiot never
meets his deadlines.
The editor who lives
for her job, Yu Yoneda.
No, you're not listening.
She's an extremely
productive person.
Yoneda!
All of these captions
are off by a line!
I'm sorry!
I'll fix it right away, sir!
It won't happen again, I swear.
Must be tough being her.
I apologize for
my incompetence!
Oh.
Hey there.
Yoneda's been waiting for you?
Then let her keep waiting,
I'll come when I'm ready.
Man, last night, huh?
Those guys we showed
up with really caused
a heck of a lot
of trouble, didn't they?
What's this now?
Don't tell me you're actually
making some new friends!
Don't go there, Shu.
Look, those guys are just-
Never mind, this has nothing
to do with you, okay?
Oh, come on, it sounds like
a really awesome story.
Don't leave anything out;
you can trust me, dude.
Must be nice being you, huh?
Yeah.
It is, actually.
Look, Tamaizumi.
That's former
porn starlet Tama Izumi?
This girl definitely had
three square meals a day.
But it wasn't food
she was munching on.
No sir.
Hold on.
Do you know her or something?
Not really; Yoneda asked me
to review her book.
Oh, I see.
Then maybe you should go over
there and introduce yourself.
Yeah, you're right.
I wonder what kinda' stuff
she likes to talk about?
Oh, you know.
The usual girlie stuff.
Just look her
in the eyes and be yourself.
While you're at it, I'd throw
a few jokes in there, too.
Whaddaya mean,
like party jokes or somethin'?
No, the same kind
of stuff that Karuo tells.
You know, the dirty,
sexual stuff.
No, I can't,
I don't know her!
But, you know her,
don't you, Kakeru?
Introduce me already!
Why are you
being such an asshole?
Come on, man!
Be like Karuo.
Be like Karuo!
Alright!
I'll be like Karuo!
I've only heard it
second hand, so tell me.
Female perverts.
Are they real or just fantasy?
Excuse me?
Smooth operator!
Look, I'm almost certain
you know this already,
and forgive me if this comes
across as condescending,
but even if you
didn't mean it that way,
sexual harassment
is sexual harassment.
Epic fail!
I am so sorry about that!
I'm not a pervert,
my name's Shusuke and I'm
a freelance writer!
I know you; you're the
famous Tama Izumi, right?
Oh, well yes, that's me!
Sir, I apologize
for my behavior,
I've never been
called famous before!
Oh, goodness me,
I really am so sorry.
This is way different
from what Kakeru told me.
Have you ever heard
of 'Men's Freeze?'
It's the men's periodical
published by Shogensha.
Um... Yes.
I work freelance for
them from time to time,
and they've asked me to write
a review of your latest book.
No way!
Oh, gosh, there's
really no need to stand.
Anyway, I just
happened to spot you
sitting over here by yourself,
and thought I should pop over
and say hi to a fellow writer.
Uh, hey Miss,
is everything okay?
I'm so happy,
thank you very much!
Uh, Bowing's
not really necessary.
Please, just relax
and have a seat, okay?
I wonder, would a girl like this
really dig Karuo's dirty talk?
He's giving me the 'go' sign?
Um, well then.
There's something
I'd really like to ask you.
Yes, ask me anything, please!
So, what color panties
do you have on today?
I see.
Am I safe to assume
this is the direction
your article will take?
Uh, well.
It is a men's
magazine after all, so-
Is that a fact?
My panties are white.
Actually, that's not right.
My panties are beige.
Oh, really,
they're, beige, huh?
How scandalous!
Wait, I look like
a total idiot, here.
This conversation is going
nowhere, Is this girl really a-
He's just been messing with me!
Sir?
Yeah. What's up?
To be completely honest,
it doesn't make much difference
to me how you
present the article.
Huh?
See, the thing is, all I really
want is for as many people
as possible to read my book.
So, if your story can help
with that, then please, just
write whatever you want to!
I will do everything I can.
You know what, Kakeru,
you're a real jerk!
Hmm?
Well, you two guys
are here pretty early,
I guess that means
you're excited
about tonight's festivities?
The singles' party is tonight?
Look at you, Mr. Cool,
acting like this whole
thing is just old hat.
Sorry, but your right hand,
porno and lotion don't count,
virgin!
Hey!
I'm not a virgin!
So, what's the story
on that girl you said
you'd invite to the party?
Don't you worry, guys.
Truth is, I've been out
there looking for some
really good tail
to take Mochizuki's place.
And I've gotten replies
from some of my former staff.
Your former staff?
I don't know any of them, do I?
One of them is a student and an
author named Hiyoko Tamaizumi.
Wait, Tama Izumi?
No, no, 'Tamaizumi.'
Oh!
So the girl in glasses
I met earlier?
Yeah, that's the one.
Hiyoko Tamaizumi.
So this book's not--?!
Not by Hiyoko Tamaizumi.
But--
I need to use your phone!
He sure can be dense
sometimes, can't he?
How could I not have
picked up on this sooner?
It seems so obvious now
that I think about it!
Boy, do I feel like the
dumbest guy in the stairwell.
Oh man!
I said I was going
to write that article!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Now I have to ask Yu
to let me write a piece
about Hiyoko Tamaizumi, too!
Uh, they really
are beige, aren't they?
Hey, yo!
Is everyone havin'
a good time ?!
'Cause it's Saturday night,
boys and girls!
Yeah!
Alexander, rock on!
Right on, Shusuke,
you're so awesome!
I'm so wasted, and I'm
gonna drink 'till I puke!
So, Tamaizumi.
You still putting out
books that won't sell,
causing publishers to leap
out of their office windows?
Yes, thank you for asking, and
I assume that you're floating
through life aimlessly like
the complete waste of space
you are, is that an
accurate summation?
All right, let's get
things rolling here!
Yes, it's time for-'Shine!
The third
"Good luck Kinako" event,
special party number threeeeee!
Please, leave the
emcee duties to me, folks!
Spreading joy and
merriment is what I do best!
I'd also like an opportunity
to explain myself to Hiyoko.
First, let's get all the
introductions out of the way,
right?
Here's the girl
this night's all about!
You mean me?
I'm eating.
A little more, please!
Well, I'm sorry,
but this food's delicious.
Hi, I'm Kinako Mochizuki!
And what do you think,
Mr. Head Judge?
We've got some
pieces of ass out there,
but they're lacking
when it comes to romance.
Yes, romance!
"Romans"?
What about 'em?
Is that on the test?
Just shut up!
Show us how it's
done already, jerk!
But of course.
Well, good evening ladies,
my name is Karuo.
My job is making sweet love.
I like naughty romance
and sinful seduction!
I'll give you something to
eat you'll never ever forget.
Whenever you're in need, I'll
fill you up every single time!
Oh yes, I know the kama sutra.
And I can go all night.
Let's hear it, folks!
Did he really just say
he would 'fill me up?'
I'm pretty sure he was
being metaphysical.
Come on, what are you
doing, do you really think
you're qualified
to be judging romance?
Well.
Yes, I do, thank you
so much for asking.
I am a hopeless
romantic, oh yeah.
Hey.
Wait a second, did you
just laugh at me, Hiyoko?
If that's how
they're going to be.
Good evening, ladies and
gentlemen, I'm Shusuke and I
came here on a white horse
from the land of auroras
to help keep true love alive!
You wanna guess my profession?
I'm known as the Artisan
of glass slippers.
My hobby is counting
the stars in your eyes.
And I like to add 'try it'
to the end of sentences,
even when it makes no sense!
And you should know, the animal
I like the most is the Pegasus.
Hold on, you just laughed.
So does that mean that
you like the Pegasus too?
That's right!
She laughed!
Please, who cares, at her age,
they'll laugh at anything!
Oooo, does this mean
he's after Hiyoko?
For her sake, I hope not!
Oh, come on, give me
a break, you guys!
See that look on her face,
it's as if she's gonna throw up
in her mouth, she couldn't
hide that if she tried!
They might actually
be a good couple.
So.
Spill the beans; how do you
really feel about Hiyoko?
Huh?
Well uh, I've been a big fan
of Miss Tamaizumi's books
for quite a while now,
and I think her latest one
is really interesting too.
Not that I've
read it yet, but hey.
Oh, well, that's extremely
kind of you to say.
Do you really mean
that or are you just
saying that to get laid?
What?
Her book.
The latest one's the
super dark one, isn't it?
Come on now, if you're
really a fan of her work,
you should be able to tell her
what you really think.
What's wrong with you?
You know he can't say things
like that in front of her.
Why not?
If he doesn't say it
to her right now,
he'd be talking about
her behind her back.
I got a plan.
I think we should
talk about hot pants.
This guy's onto something!
Long live hot pants,
am I right?
Speaking of hot pants,
I'm a fan of shirts
being tucked into them,
how about you?!
Aww, that was really sweet.
Doing my part, sir, leaving them
un-tucked is throwing pearls
before swine, or worse!
I think swine is too classy!
As far as color goes,
I like navy blue!
I've never known anyone who
talks about hot pants like that.
Yeah, well,
those two are perverts.
For the rest of my adult life
I want to live at a hot spring,
drinking hot toddies,
eating hot dogs,
and loving those hot pants!
Hot pants are the only
pants I'm interested in!
Because I've got
the hots for hot pants!
As far as I'm concerned,
that's fine;
no one here is stopping you.
Shut up, woman!
Don't talk to me until you put
on some navy blue hot pants!
And don't forget
to tuck in your shirt.
Whatever, you guys are
just a bunch of perverts.
Since you like hot pants
so much, go put some on,
you big jerk.
You're absolutely right,
they are perverts.
There's no doubt
left in my mind.
Just you remember this, Writings
from antiquity tell us,
devils with buckets and knives
will visit people's houses
at night, exclaiming,
'give me hot pants',
And those devil dudes
will be really pissed
when there are none!
Hey, let's make the
girls put on hot pants.
Where hot pants?
None here.
Uh, yes there are,
over there.
For real?
I'll be right back!
Wow, that was fun.
That the world may know peace.
This thing on?
Tell me when
we're rolling, okay?
I can't wait to see
those babes in bikinis,
they really get me going.
What?
We are rolling?
Oh, come on,
you can't use this;
I'm trying to sell
a clean image here.
You want me fired or what?
Back it up and take it
from the top.