Multiple personalities.
So that's it.
Yes, exactly!
The main character
in this game has
multiple personality disorder.
You're not really
Takashi, are you?
Uh.
No, I'm not.
Sorry.
I thought not.
It's kind of difficult to
explain, but if I told you
that I was dreaming
and talking in my sleep,
would you take my word for it?
Well.
I'm not so sure.
The truth is, I've seen
this sort of thing before,
and I've known something was
going on for a long time.
I mean, let's not forget that
I am his girlfriend after all.
Well, you could say that.
Listen, I don't want to stick my
nose in where it doesn't belong.
But I do feel for him,
and I understand what he's
going through in a way
that most people couldn't.
Is that a roundabout way of
saying, 'I'm on your side,
so tell me more?'
Come on, don't be like that.
We can help each other.
Oh, is that a fact?
It is.
In a way, I'm in the exact
same situation that he's in.
Right.
If you help me out by
telling me everything you know,
I'll be more than happy
to return the favor.
Fine.
But I want something, too.
Whatever you do, don't
tell Takashi about this.
Wait.
What do you mean?
Why not?
Here's the deal.
He doesn't even know
we're a part of him
and I'd prefer
to keep it that way.
Something tells me he
wouldn't take it very well.
All right, fine.
I won't say a word.
Not good enough.
Swear it.
I swear to you on
the life of my brother
who is no longer with us.
Okay!
How about a proper
introduction then?
My name is Shusuke Chitose.
A lot of people call me
'Slippery Shusuke'
for some weird reason.
But, truth be told, I don't know
whether to be highly offended
or flattered by that.
Anyway, I am very pleased
to make your acquaintance.
Well, Shusuke.
It's nice to meet you too.
Marvelous!
Man, I can't believe you
let the cat out of the bag.
Yeah, well.
It just happened.
You jerk!
Don't stand there
and play dumb with me.
What the hell do you think we've
been working our butts off
for this whole time, huh?!
Dude, she's Takashi's
girlfriend,
will you please relax?!
There's no way
he has a girlfriend!
That's not cool.
It'd hurt his feelings
if he heard you say that.
But what about you, Hayato?
You seem like you've
had something new
on your mind lately.
You've got your eye set on
some lucky lady, don't ya?
No.
Where in the world would you
get a dumb idea like that?
I don't need anybody.
But I guess I could
ask you the same thing.
What about all those girls
you've been working with lately?
Look, man,
Hiyoko is my superior;
we work together
and that's all!
Wait, her?
I don't think that's
gonna end very well.
Stupid me!
Now I'm gonna have
to do everything I can
to find out the girl you like.
And once I trick you
into telling me,
you're gonna
feel like an idiot!
Ha!
Come on.
Who is it?
Spill the beans, buddy!
You're really starting
to get on my nerves, man!
And don't change the subject!
I wanna know why in the hell
you're running around town
telling our secret to
people who have no business
knowing about it!
It's no big deal.
There isn't much time
left anyway.
I told her because Asuka
said that she wanted
to help out Takashi.
She did?
I guess I gotta few things
to take care of, huh?
Tell me about it.
But as far as you and I are
concerned, we'll keep going on
like we always have, and try
not to ruffle any feathers.
Sounds good.
But what are we
supposed to do about Takashi?
Right.
He still hasn't come back
from Gretegard yet.
He's been there
for a really long time.
So what now?
Only one thing to do.
All right.
Let's play for it!
Rock, paper-!
Scissors!
Morning Kobato!
Oh, hey.
How are you this
morning, Mr. Chitose?
I'm great, just a little
hungry, that's all.
Well, breakfast
is almost ready.
Wow.
Impressive.
I can't believe you
actually remembered
that I hate asparagus.
Also, there's plenty of curry,
but it's all left over
from last night.
Hey, that's okay by me.
I think curry's
even better the next day.
Uh, Shusuke.
'You know who', has something
bad happened to him?
Oh, do you mean Takashi?
No, it's the same
as it always is,
he's just staying
a little longer this time.
Don't worry,
everything is gonna be fine,
Hayato and I will cover
for him in any way we can.
So it's just you
and Mr. Narita then?
Is that all?
What do you mean?
What about Mr. Itami?
Who's that? Oh! Karura!
Don't worry; I doubt he'll
be coming out anymore.
There's nothing for you
to be concerned about.
Besides, the world's
a much better place
when that rambunctious piece
of work stays hidden away.
It's happened several
times before, you know?
There were others besides big
brother and 'you know who',
that were here one day
and then just gone the next.
Vanished.
In a blink of an eye,
they disappeared like
they were never there.
Please, don't worry.
Everything's fine.
Good morning, everyone.
Get this!
Oh, sorry about that, buddy.
No, no don't worry about me.
You smacked your hand
pretty hard, are you sure
you're gonna be
all right, friend?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just be low-key,
act like Takashi
and everything'll be a-okay.
Hey, I didn't know
we were in the same class.
Yeah, I guess we are.
You're really
eating bread for lunch?
Uh. You know, the cafeteria
is always so busy.
I bought this on the way here.
What's up, do you wanna
split this with me?
No. I'm all set.
It's fascinating. Just when
I think I've met all of them,
here's another one
who pops up out of the blue.
Uh, what do you mean?
Oh, I'm just
thinking out loud.
Okay. That sure was weird.
Takashi! Takashi! Takashi!
What's up Takashi?!
Uh. Hey. Who're you?
Oh, come on now,
you silly goose,
you know exactly who I am!
--I'm Miyako Yamashina!
--Don't hit me. That hurts!
Yesterday was
absolutely wonderful!
I was so touched! So
thrilled! So moved to tears!
I never imagined
in my wildest dreams
that you would
be so bold. Wow!
I'm so glad I
finally approached you!
Good job, Miyako!
Uh. Awesome?
I don't know if you know this,
but it was my first time too.
My heart was pounding
like crazy but you were
so sweet and gentle.
Uh, I don't know why
you're making that face?
Yesterday I was
an innocent little girl,
but today I woke up a woman!
And all because
I gave myself to you!
Oh, Takashi,
what have you done?!
Last night, I could
barely keep my eyes closed
thinking about
how romantic you were.
All I wanted to do was hold
you tight and squeeze you
till your head
popped right off!
Then, I couldn't stand
it anymore so I had to
do something about it, I felt
flushed. Oh, so flushed.
Like I was gonna explode,
and so I did it.
Wait Did it? Whadja do?
I read our fortune!
See?
I checked our compatibility
and we're a solid pair!
I tried flowers, stars, animals,
even tortoise shell divination
and every single time we came
out a completely perfect match!
It's really cool that
you talked to me for so long!
It's been quite a while
since I've had somebody
I could get so close
to like that!
Thanks for taking the
time to make me feel
as though I really matter!
It's so nice not to worry about
having to try and fit in!
Man.
And here I thought Takashi
lived the regular old boring,
life of a high school kid,
but boy was I wrong.
Looks like Asuka's not the only
person I have to watch out for.
Hey, you.
I really don't appreciate you
sneaking up on me like that;
and I'm not a stranger,
I already told you my name,
remember?
Shunosuke.
It's just Shusuke.
Just Shusuke.
Strike the just and then
what does that leave?
Shunosuke.
I already told you,
there's no 'no' in there.
Shusuke.
It's Shusuke!
Gesundheit.
Take two aspirin and
call me in the morning!
Thanks a lot, folks,
we'll be here all week!
So tell me.
Why in the heck has Shusuke
been front and center
since this morning?
It's kind of a long story.
Any possible way I could
speak to the real deal?
Unfortunately, no,
he's a little late
getting back this time.
I mean, you're supposed to limit
your gaming to one hour per day.
So, when is he coming back?
I'm afraid I don't
have that information.
Listen: I want to speak
to him right now, got it?
Not possible.
But, at the risk
of being presumptuous,
you could pretend I'm him.
Funny. But you know?
I'm wondering if smacking you
upside the head might make him
come back a little sooner.
Hey, there's no need
to be angry.
Ya' know, I never would've
taken you for the violent type.
I'm glad that's over!
Oh yeah, I feel much more
comfortable in my own skin!
Let's show'em what
Shusuke Chitose is made of.
That's right, I'm the man!
Yeah, would you
be quiet, please?
Okay.
Hey guys, you gotta second?
There's something important
I've been meaning to tell you.
So. As you
undoubtedly know already,
Christmas Eve
is coming up very soon.
Uh yeah.
We've heard.
For most, it's a holy night
of joy and celebration.
But for those of us in
the restaurant business,
it's a fight to the finish!
That said, I wanna make sure
we have more customers
at Alexander than any
other joint in town,
so I've devised a
plan! And here it is!
A healthy dose of 't and a',
brought to you by our very own
pop supergroup!
And We are the 'Alex 2'!
We did it!
Our big moment to shine in
the spotlight's finally here!
Hey. Don't cry.
We're pop stars,
we're supposed to be smiling!
You're so right.
Thank you Eriko!
We worship you!
You're the best!
You're so hot!
We love you!
What a bunch of losers.
I need a break.
I swear, I'm a business genius!
From now on, these
two hotties are gonna
do all of my
promotions and events!
What better way to kick off
Christmas than a live concert?!
Oh yeah, this rocks!
This show is so bad ass!
Tops off! Tops off!
This is pretty amazing.
I know. We're
totally pop stars!
Sir, I've got a good idea!
I go by 'Producer' now.
Whatever you say,
Mr. Producer sir!
In all of this excitement I
think you might have forgotten
about your top secret weapon!
Put me in producer Daddy,
Shusuke's ready to get down!
Good call, son, people have
been asking for that lately.
Get off the stage!
Take it easy, guys!
Come on; don't knock it
till you try it!
Shusuke, get back
to work right now!
Peace, yo!
I mean, really. These people.
But Kinako, you quit working
here to study for your exams,
didn't you?
If you come here every day and
goof around, what's the point?
Aww, c'mon don't say that.
Besides, I brought something
with me to read today,
check it out.
Oh, right.
That just went on sale.
Yep, it sure did.
And that review you wrote on
Hiyoko's book is featured in it.
See, look. It's right here.
Oh yeah. Wow.
I'll read it out loud.
"If I had to compare this
book to something I'd say
it's like a nice stroll
along a nature trail."
"The visual imagery that emerges
from the matter of fact
depiction exudes emotional
sentiment and depth."
Stop it, you're
embarrassing me.
It's weird hearing
someone else read my words.
"The material may be
difficult to approach,
but once you've committed,
you'll be hooked and
the deeper significance
will reveal itself".
How 'bout that?
Well, whaddaya think?
You've got a real talent
for delivering praise!
It's true, I thought
the exact same thing!
Wow, thanks a lot!
As a matter of fact,
your write-up makes me
want to go out and pick up
a copy of the book right now!
That's the whole point,
you totally should!
Nah. Once I read it,
I'll just be disappointed.
Huh, why is that?
Well, because I don't wanna read
a story about some old geezer.
Oh no, there's a lot more to it.
Trust me, once you get into the
story you won't put it down,
it's like sipping
a fine wine or something.
Whaddaya think, Kinako?
Well, I don't know.
Umm, I thought her last book was
entertaining and fun to read.
But to be honest, this one
just isn't my cup of tea.
And besides.
If you are gonna have an old man
as your main character.
You at least have to flesh it
out by making him realistic.
Hers was one dimensional,
and it was clearly written
by young person.
Yeah but,
she is a young person,
she can't do
anything about that.
Plus, as a writer, I think her
desire to explore new frontiers
and try something outside
of her comfort zone
shows a lot of promise.
Desire alone isn't what
sells books, and you know it.
Right?
No one is buying it.
Isn't that true?
Well, uh-
So maybe she should stop
over-reaching and go back
to writing romantic
comedies for younger girls
like she did before.
That's the stuff
people wanna read anyway.
Hiyoko?
You didn't hear our
conversation, did you?
Thank you very much.
I will take your feedback
and constructive criticisms
to heart in my future writings.
Uh...
Sure thing.
And there goes
that attitude again.
I have no idea
what you mean by that?
Come on, you can't
play stupid with me.
Oh well.
I guess the days of you being
fun to be around are long gone,
aren't they?
If you'll excuse me.
Hiyoko, wait!
Look, there might have been
a few parts that bothered me.
But still, I liked it.
It's a really great book!
Don't be discouraged.
Keep writing.
That was so rude.
There's a much nicer way to give
someone criticism, you know?
Please, she'll be fine.
You have to be blunt with her,
it's the only thing
she responds to.
Yeah but still.
Your critiques on her book
were pretty specific
and very well thought out.
You read it closely.
Nah.
You guys. I gotta
be honest with you,
if we don't find it soon,
I'm afraid it'll never turn up!
No, we have to keep looking!
--We can't give up yet!
--Hey! There you are!
So, what is it?
Whaddaya want? This better
not be a waste of our time,
or I'll make you regret it.
You guys are looking
for Naru's bicycle, right?
Well, I think I found it!
Look, Naru, this is totally it.
Looks like our search
is finally over, huh?!
Oh. It is the right color.
But that's not my bike.
No? Are you sure?
Absolutely.
They're very similar,
but this one isn't right.
I mean, for one thing mine's got
a backrest behind the seat.
I could've sworn this was it.
By the way Ai, why are you out
here looking for her bike,
what's in it for you?
There's nothing in it
for me, thank you.
Other than giving
a hand to a good friend
who obviously
needs a little help.
And besides we are the
neighborhood watch group.
Yanigahara Flame Birdes
to the rescue!
Stop right there, loser town!
Check yourself
before you wreck yourself!
Oh Great.
Eww. Yuk.
Lock up your daughters
and hide yo mammas folks
cause R-Wing's here
to rock tha house!
Beat it you jackwads!
Take it easy there, pretty boy.
We're not here to get in your
way, so just calm down,
all right?
It's all good.
As a matter of fact,
we want to thank you.
Hey there, man.
Dark and angry.
Me?
Yeah! You're Hayato
Narita, right?
You're the one who kicked
the livin' crap out of
the Archbishop
for us, aren't you?!
Yeah. So what?
We just wanna say thanks.
That guy was starting to rub us
the wrong way to say the least.
Yeah.
But since you beat him down
and dropped the hammer
on that evil scumbag,
you have to take his place.
You're the chosen one who's
been sent here to lead us
to a new paradise.
Hayato! You are
the coolest, man!
You mind if
I call you 'my bro'?
Please! Pretty please!
I mind a lot, actually.
All right then, but we all owe
you big time for doing that.
As thanks, how about we
help you look for that bike?
After everything you've done for
us, it's the least we can do.
Hey bro. You just take it
easy and enjoy hangin' out
with those two pretty ladies;
we've got it covered from here!
What's up with
those freakin' weirdos?
Whoa. Did you hear that?
Yeah, of course I did.
We'd better get going and
tell LR and the others!
Looks like it's
us against them.
There's no way in hell
I'm gonna let those jerks
find that bike first!
Damn right.
YFB versus R-Wing, round two.
This is our chance
to show those jerks who's boss.
Yeah, I can't wait!
You two wait for us
at Pal Crepe.
We'll get in touch with you
the second we find it!
Right. We've got this!
Bye, bye!
Well, they're off
to the races.
Whatever, come on.
We should get going.
Wait a second, are you
absolutely sure about this boss?
The rest of the members are
out looking for Naru's bike.
Of course I am.
At least it'll kill
a little bit of time, right?
Yes sir.
How 'bout that.
Finding your bike's turned into
quite an ordeal, hasn't it?
Sure has.
It's weird. I wanna
know why these losers
have so much time
on their hands.
What does it matter?
At least it's healthier
than shooting each other
under overpasses, right?
They find bike, Naru.
They find it for certain.
Hope so. Thanks for
the support, Alice.
Hey. Wait.
What's up?
I don't understand. What's
so special about that bike?
If you can't find it, why don't
we just get you a new one?
The truth is,
it's not the bike I want.
I mean, the bike's great,
but there's something
in the front basket
I really need to get back.
It must be something
that's very important to you.
Oh yeah. I have
to have my pager.
What's pager?
Lame.
There's nothing lame about it!
Pocket-bell pagers are
the best; I've used them
since I was a little kid.
Let's see, how can
I put this delicately:
No one uses pagers anymore.
Yeah.
Don't you think it's about time
you upgraded to a cell phone?
People are going to think
there's something wrong
with you if you
keep using that.
That's okay,
I don't need a cell phone.
I don't have any
friends to text,
call or email with, anyway.
And besides,
I love it so much.
That pager was
a gift from my mother.
Things were always rocky
at home and so, growing up,
I had to live
apart from my mom.
I missed her a whole lot,
but she gave me that pager,
it's the only way that we
can keep in touch, ya know?
I see.
Hey, Drac.
Get out there
and find that thing.
No matter what
it takes, you hear me?
Done.
I will tell papa
about it as well.
And then. We will find
beeping device because.
The nation need know.
Uh, I really don't see
how this is a matter
of international concern.
You wrong. Big time crime
lord peoples are behind this
for definite,
I know it to be true.
Huh?
I see them do
their badness before.
A grouping of bad men
that park in front of Jim's
stand and load up bunches
of wheely bikes into
pick-up trucks and
steal them all away.
Oh, no, no, no.
They're not crime lords,
they work for the city.
That's just what they do.
Their job is to pick up
abandoned objects like bicycles
so the streets aren't
all cluttered with stuff.
Hey, they sweep the streets
quite a bit, don't they?
They do? I didn't know that.
Naru. You did check with
the city ward's office
to see if they
have your bike, right?
No. I gotta be honest,
I didn't even know
the city ward's office existed.
Seriously.
Well.
I guess that was a really
stupid move on my part.
What is city ward?
Come on now, sun,
that's just ridiculous.
You're seriously getting
on my nerves, buddy.
Still, I think it's kinda nice.
Huh? What is?
Oh, you know, getting to spend
some time with you like this.
Yeah. If you say so.
Hey! This is it! This
is my bicycle! Wow!
Uh-oh.
I just realized we forgot to
get in touch with the others.
It's over, losers!
Haven't you scumbags
given up yet?!
You are sadly
mistaken douche-bag!
Admit defeat!
What? There's no way
you could ever beat us!
Oh yeah? Bring it on!
--You're going down, R-Wing!
--You're going down, YFB!
It's here! Now that I've
got you back in my arms,
I'm never letting you
outta my sight ever again,
--no matter what!
--Good for you.
Hey! It means a lot to me
that you went out of
your way to help me find it!
Well, uh. It's no big deal.
What's wrong?
Oh. It's nothing really.
All right. Tell the truth.
You got another message,
didn't you?
What'd it say;
I'm just dyin to know!
Oh. You are? Well, then.
How about this?
We'll race back and
if you win, I'll tell.
Hey! Wait!
You know there's no way
I can beat you on foot!
Plus, I'm way out of shape
and I really hate running!
Come back here!
Then I guess you'll never know;
hey maybe you should get a bike!
That's it!
Then we could all go out
and ride our bicycles together.
We'll invite Ai,
and the Crepe Lady...
Ah, man. Slow down a little,
will ya? I'm gonna puke!
Wow, it's gonna be so much
fun! Where should we go?
Hayato, where do you
think we should go?!
If I don't stop running,
I'm not going anywhere
cause I'm about
to friggin' drop dead!
Oh, you're such a silly boy!
I love hanging out with you!
I'm now accepting
your CONDORlences.
This is the late DJ Condor
still coming at you today
from the depths of Naraku.
The Condor's the only DJ
that can spin great records
from the great beyond.
So send me your letters
of CONDORlence and when
you visit my grave,
make sure you bring flowers.