Okay, why not?
Go out with me!
So, you're Takashi, right?
I'm Asuka Watarai.
It's nice to meet you.
Yeah.
Same to you.
So where exactly were
you wanting to go today?
Movies?
OB GYN appointment?
Or maybe just
a little shopping?
That's not what I meant!
Um, I was trying
to tell you that I like you
and I want to be with you.
But I chose
the wrong words, I guess!
That makes sense!
Thought so!
Well, see ya!
Uh.
Just a second!
Yeah?
Well.
Uh, I don't want you
to freak out or anything,
but I think people have
the wrong idea about us.
They-
They think you're
my boyfriend, right?
Yeah, um, I'm sorry.
Wait!
You knew?!
Then why didn't you-?
Because I'm awesome like that.
I knew if people
thought we were together
then they wouldn't
pick on you so much.
Pick on me?
Oh, sorry.
They weren't
trying to be jerks.
It was all in good fun,
I promise.
That's just how I joke with
my friends sometimes, y'know?
Then I guess this
just got a little awkward.
Sorry.
Please.
Don't apologize.
Wait, why aren't you
freaking out right now?
People are saying some
messed up things about you!
I see.
There's somebody else?
Um, no, not even
close to that.
Well that's a relief!
So, we can keep things as
they are for awhile, right?
I mean, yeah?
And that was that.
It's been a little over
two years since Takashi Haneda
and Asuka Watarai
began their little romance,
if you can even call it that.
I saw that!
Oh, please.
I don't buy it.
You were looking up
her skirt just now.
It was obvious.
I was not.
You're making that up!
What?!
Are you calling me a liar?
You trying to say
I'm seeing things?
Yeah, is that why you're about
to piss yourself, Pervert?
Well, you don't
have to convince me.
I mean, unless you were
checking me out, too.
In which case, no thanks.
You're not my type.
No.
You've got it wrong.
I wasn't looking at anyone.
Liar!
This is not the most
ideal time to be summoned.
I've got to clear up this
misunderstanding first.
What's going on over here?
Is there a problem?
I caught this jerk
looking up your skirt
while you were walking.
What?!
Not true.
He said it's 'not true.'
Of course he did!
No perv is ever gonna
come out and say 'yup!
You caught me.'
Even if it was true,
it wouldn't bother me.
Meet my boyfriend.
Huh?!
Hey.
What's up?
Sorry for the confusion,
but thanks anyway!
Uh, no, I should
be apologizing.
Forgive me.
That's very nice,
but he's the one you insulted.
Right.
This sucks.
I'm very sorry!
You know that's why people
think you're a push-over?
I mean, do you ever get mad?
Of course I do.
But he was only trying
to look out for you.
I mean, what if I
really was looking?
Yeah right.
Oh well. I guess it's all
just part of your charm.
Tell the truth.
Did you see them?
You're dead if you did.
And I'll know if
you're lying to me about it.
You're really close
to me right now.
Hey, Haneda!
Oh, hey Miss Takauchi!
This whole 'graduation essay'
thing has me really bummed out.
Teach said we had
to start prepping for them.
So, how far have you
gotten or have you
just been dickin' around?
Oh.
I guess, I haven't started yet.
Yeah, I figured.
We need to have
a class meeting or something
and make a plan--I don't want
to be stressing about this
last minute.
Yeah, I agree.
So let's find a place
to hang out at after school
and talk about it?
You want to go some place
after school and 'talk?'
You mean like your
house?! The hell?!
Are you trying
to get me to bang you?
That was some good
strategy tho, almost had me...
We would've been all alone
at your place and then- Wait.
You dick, I'm not gonna
be your stand-in Asuka!
You're totally wrong!
I have no desire
to do that with you!
Oh really!
Then do it by yourself!
That's not what I meant.
Not to mention,
you're a class officer so-
Nah.
It's whatever.
I've got my hands full.
I gotta write stuff
on the board and shop.
This is all you.
Good luck!
Wait!
So you're not
even gonna help?!
It's sick how easy
you got out of that!
Yeah, I'm a little
jealous--not gonna lie!
What do you mean?
That was crafty delegation.
Again so soon?
Man, I guess they must
really need me right now.
Huh?
Where am I?
I see.
The court summoner has
requested my presence.
The war has begun.
Lord Hawk!
Lord Hawk has
finally returned!
We've been waitin'
for you, Sir Hawk!
Welcome back!
Sir Pegasus,
you've done quite well
protecting Beltmond
in my absence.
You have my utmost gratitude.
At last you return
to us, Hawk Cyan-Blue.
Princess Asuka!
Successor to the royal
bloodline of Gretagard
and our sole princess,
how great to see you.
I am overjoyed.
I, Sir Hawk Cyan-Blue, have
returned and am at your service.
I pray thee, tell me true:
what errors have occurred during
my absence, Sweet Princess?
It is the army of the
evil realm being led
by the hateful
Yokujin soldiers.
They are moving quickly
toward the north forest.
The goblin and orc ground
forces have also begun
to advance.
This war is not
progressing well, I'm afraid.
Goblins?
But what of our
army's reinforcements?
My heart weighs heavily,
but it is you.
You are our last reinforcement
and regretfully our only hope.
It's true.
Even the Four Feathers
have gone.
Our successors.
What is to become of the throne
if we do not survive this?
Garuda the Wise
has been captured,
and both
"The Eternal Wing" Eagle
and "Lord of the Underworld"
Falcon have been missing
for quite some time now.
We are falling apart.
And our land.
All that remains are the remote
areas of the countryside!
Good fortune is with us.
We now have the strongest
warrior of the Four Feathers
of ten thousand Colors,
the Golden Hawk, our friend,
Hawk Cyan-Blue!
I await your orders,
my lovely princess.
Sir Hawk.
I order you in the name
of Gretagard's royal family
to lend your
support to our allies.
Battle against the Yokujin
soldiers in the North Forest.
Our gratitude and
prayers are with you.
Leuchten Greta.
By the holy sword,
Gretacaliber, bestowed on me,
by His Majesty the King,
I vow to complete
the mission Princess
Asuka has appointed me!
Yeaaah!
My Brave Hawk Cyan-Blue,
fair well in battle,
but please stay strong for me.
My heart shall remain tortured
until you are safely returned
to my side.
Eagle, Falcon, Garuda.
I wonder.
Are we looking at the same
mournful stars this night?
O, that the world
may know peace.
I guess that means
I can definitely
be summoned at school.
I shouldn't be complaining.
I'm glad they know where
to find me when they need me.
Shit.
I'm sorry!
Where did you get it?
I'll go buy you
another one right now.
I know you.
Eh.
Um, you're Haryu, aren't you?
And you are?
Takashi Haneda from Class 3-A.
I'm an officer too,
for the class, 3A.
Takashi Haneda?
Right.
You're Asuka's friend,
aren't you?
I get it now.
It's all making sense.
That's what
caught Asuka's eye.
She's always had
quite the nose for it.
What does that even mean?
Huh? Oh.
Well, there's something
special about her,
but I'm sworn to secrecy,
so that's all I'm gonna say.
Things could
actually start to get
very interesting around here.
Damn.
No room for mistakes now,
but that can't be helped.
I might as well just
slit open your stomach
and dig out that
gem you swallowed.
What do you say, Pal?
Totally kidding.
So, are you saying
that you and Asuka-?
I said I can't talk
about that, didn't I?
Oh, right, I remember.
You know, the fact that
Asuka has chosen you
arouses my curiosity.
But on a more personal level-
I'm sorry, but you are
not worthy of any feeling
I may have, aside from apathy.
I find your lack
of courage insulting.
No. Wait, I take it back.
I do feel something for you:
you make me want to vomit.
All over your face.
Not again.
What is going on today?
Behold!
Towering before us is the most
impregnable Zwei Fortress.
Above us, a thousand
yokujin soldiers!
On the ground,
ten thousand monsters!
Yet we fear not;
for we have Hawk on our side!
We give our glory to Gretagard!
Leuchten Greta!
Sir Hawk!
Isn't it amazing how quickly
we've amassed this many allies?
Every last person here holds
you in the highest regard.
Surely you know by now you are
like a savior in their eyes.
You flatter me, Pegasus.
Though I've been honored with
the title 'Wings of Gold'
long enough, it still makes
me feel shy to receive
such praise in
front of so many.
Even so, I am grateful for
your kindness and generosity.
If there's one thing
we can't praise you for,
it's this modesty that
makes you blush like a lady.
Yet, strangely it's one of the
traits I admire most about you.
Ah!
Vernar, the "Arrow of Light!"
How about that!
The lone warrior of the
mountains who is known
for his isolation
has joined our ranks!
Only the honored Hawk
has that sort of power!
Can it be that he
also brought Andre,
the "White Flame" with him!
How noble you are, Sir,
to leave the front line
your land and commander
just to fight with us!
Our Sir Hawk is a man
of virtue and honor, indeed!
Good-day Bard,
the Gale-Force Vassal!
It is an honor to be
serving with you.
T'is an honor that you have
joined us after suffering
the kidnapping of your
son which left you at
the mercy of our enemy.
Our Sir Hawk is a pillar
of honor and virtue.
You heard them!
We are all prepared
to join in battle!
And we shall follow you
to the depths of Hell
if you command it!
Sir Hawk!
Praise Sir Hawk!
All hands, charge!
The time between the summonings
is getting shorter every day.
I can't control
the time or location.
Maybe the end is near.
So I have to be ready.
What are you doing?
I'm cold!
Shut the door!
Sorry!
I didn't even
notice you were there.
Brother!?!
Why do you always
have to be so mean?!
I can't see,
let me get the light.
It's too bright in here!
I'm so sorry!
I just- I'm turning it off!
What happened?
Damn it, Kobato!
Put on your clothes!
Clothes?
Why?
What do you mean, "why?"
I'm not interested
in seeing my sister naked.
Sorry if that's weird to you.
So, did you see me?
No.
Thankfully I wasn't looking.
Oh, good.
I was worried.
So, you should
hurry up and change.
Uh, yeah, I know.
I was going to.
Good...
I mean, you don't want
to catch a cold or anything...
It's going around, I hear.
Thank you.
I'll be careful.
Right.
'Kay.
Bye.
I mean, Good night.
That's how it's been
lately between me
and my sister--kinda awkward.
You'd think we were strangers
but we see each other every day.
It feels more like we're
distant cousins than siblings.
I bet she wouldn't
even notice or care
if I wasn't here anymore.
Haneda residence.
I'm so sorry for
calling this late.
This is Asuka Watarai.
I'm a friend
of Takashi's from school.
Is he up by any chance?
Can I talk to him?
And that's about it.
You are a rockstar.
Thanks!
Sure.
You always study this late?
I'm surprised you called.
Is it really that weird?
I mean, I'm allowed to call
my boyfriend, aren't I?
So.
We're still?
Of course.
I mean, unless you
met someone else?
Seriously?
You haven't met
anyone else you like?
You're not blowing off other
girls because of me, are you?
You're not
obligated or anything.
We can break up
whenever you want.
Not that it'll be
the easiest thing.
I may actually be
a little sad about it.
Hello?
Are you still there?
Takashi?
Me?
Yeah.
I'm here.
What's the deal--have
you met someone new?
Prob'ly not.
I guess a girlfriend shouldn't
be asking things like that.
Uh.
It's kinda weird.
Well, whatever.
Thanks for all
your help. 'Night!
Oh.
Sure.
Good night.
She said she'd be sad
if we ever broke up.
I guess disappearing
from this world would qualify.
I wish that we would've
spent more time together.
Like I said, we're gonna
need everyone's help.
Come on guys.
Listen, please.
That's all!
Thanks for playing, you guys!
But, you just let them
go without finishing.
There was no way to get it done
before the semester was over.
So thanks for
a whole lot of nothing.
I'm sorry.
--Gah.
--Wow.
How does somebody so useless
become the class President?
You again?
Yes, Hawk Cyan-Blue.
I know you!
You're Princess Asuka's-
Yes.
She has bid me good favor to
allow me to wait on her daily.
I know your heart
belongs to the princess;
therefore I pray you'll
forgive my fervent request.
Show me your kindness.
Gaze upon me as you
do her for just as long
as the clouds shall
cover the moon.
O beautiful handmaiden,
if fortune does not allow me
to know your name,
how can I-
I won't hear any more!
You can!
Imagine it, our hearts changed.
And your affection
bestowed upon me alone.
I beg of you Sir Hawk!
You must stop!
I cannot- I mustn't-
Wow, those are pretty awesome.
Oh, compared to Asuka's?
Is that what
you're trying to say?
Of course not!
I haven't ever been
close enough to her to know
what they look like!
I like that story.
Good, there's still
a chance that I might
be able to get some!
Yeah, I don't know.
That might not be the
best idea for a lot of reasons.
The hell?!
So you got me all hot
and bothered for nothing?!
Leave it to you to pull
a fake move like that!
Please.
You're one to talk about fake.
Can you say 'implants'?
Can you say A-hole?!
These are the real deal,
when you're ticked off
you say some
pretty rude-ass things.
I'm kinda into it.
You are?
That's good to know I guess.
Well.
It's true not everyone
likes traditional romance.
Never mind!
Forget what I said!
I misspoke, fair though you are,
I cannot return your affections.
You see my heart,
and my body have-
Nice try, but you've
already said it; I heard it;
it's out there and
you can't take it back!
That's unfortunate!
Hawk!
Why does everything
suck right now?
'Right now'
only lasts a moment.
So make your next one better.
Right.
See!
It already worked!
Done, now onto
the next moment!
And I think this one
should include me.
It doesn't have to be now,
but I want to go shopping.
What do you think?
Yeah?
If not now, then when?
Um, I was hoping
to go kinda soon.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
Sure.
Oh good.
Thank you so much
for not saying 'no'.
I was a little worried.
I'd never say no!
Not to you!
Yeah.
Usually you just avoid me
so you don't ever have
to take me anywhere!
That's not always true.
For two years!
You've never once asked me
to do anything with you!
It makes me feel bad!
I shouldn't be the one
asking you out on dates!
Now wait a minute!
You were the one that said-
The thing is I don't actually
like being around people.
So the thought of dating
someone is a nightmare,
but if you're a girl who's
constantly turning every guy
down they start to hate on you,
so it's much easier if
they just think I have a
boyfriend and leave me alone.
Then there's no explaining.
You have got to be kidding me.
You're my boyfriend,
you are not the one who's
allowed to be afraid
of rejection.
Two years.
Two and a half!
If you want to take me
out then take me out!
And if you don't want
to see me anymore, that's fine!
But at least have the balls
to tell me in person!
Stop yelling.
I feel like yelling!
Deal with it!
You said you wanted people
to stay away from you.
You can't turn it
around and be mad
because I'm doing
what you said.
Oh, sure.
Take everything I said two years
ago and hold it over my head.
It's still true, though, right?
'Course not!
I'm a woman!
That the world may know peace.
Hey, Condor here.
What's up?
I wanted this week to be
a little more subdued.
So that's why I invited-
The super Sexy Hawk Cyan-Blue!
Thank you very much!
Mr. Hawk, I must say,
excellent work today.
Yes and I shall continue
to fight for peace
in Gretagard next week as well!
Actually, I don't think you'll
be joining us for awhile.