I'm sorry, Yoji, I am.
I really mean it.
Get the hell away from me,
you little thief!
You're her older brother, Yoji;
you have to protect Kobato.
Why?! Why?!
Why do you always want
to be so close to her?!
You really do love
your sister, don't you?
The two of you
get along so well.
Screw you, you little brat!
Stop it, mommy!
It's not Birdy's fault!
She didn't do anything!
Quit picking on her!
Stop! Please, mommy!
Sto-o-o-p!
Uh- are you ok?
Mother. She must've
had a weak mind, too.
After a while she just couldn't
stand living with dad anymore.
The problem was, she still
saw some of him in Yoji.
Why are you still clinging
to her, you pervert?!
That's why she
always hated seeing you,
the daughter of her brother, and
her son - more importantly,
her husband's son -
become so close.
Shall we move on?
Wait! It's ok;
you don't have to do this.
On the day I lost Gretagard,
I finally met the other
two personalities inside me, and
they told me why I was born.
I am someone's replacement.
Yoji Haneda had locked
himself away in Naraku.
The one to replace him
was to be strong, and kind,
able to always see the
light: me, Takashi Haneda.
But, like Yoji,
I too had many flaws.
When this world became
too much for me to handle,
I would flee to the world
of Gretagard, the setting
of a game I grew up playing.
I created two friends to help
in my cause, there was the
high spirited Shusuke Chitose,
and the tough-as-nails
Hayato Narita.
Neither one was thrilled about
helping me bring back Yoji,
nor confronting the past to
do so, but they ultimately
came around for Kobato's
sake, if nothing else.
Where to now?
Back home?
Do you think you could
go on a little farther?
Of course, but may I ask what
the point is? Just curious.
I think you can see
where I'm coming from.
After all, your sister Naru-
Oopsie. This ain't my van
so the steering's taking
some getting used to.
Uh- that's fine.
No problem at all.
Like I said, the fact
that you have a sister too-
Wow, these tires
have no traction!
We're sliding all over!
Fasten your seatbelts!
It hasn't changed a bit!
This church is-
Why me?
Why do you continue
doing these things?
Who keeps trying
to push us around? Who?
That was my life.
Always wanting to cry,
slowly falling apart.
I thought I was going crazy.
All I ever wanted was
for someone to save me.
Through it all, there was
someone who was so dear to me,
I had to protect her!
Tune out that static, little
man! You don't need that noise!
Forget about it! You don't have
to deal with that anymore!
It's over, don't you remember?!
My mother, she isn't-
She's gone now.
Well, um-
It's all my fault,
for what I did to her.
No one will ever forgive me
for what I've done.
It's impossible.
I have to get out of here!
That's why I ran away,
to forget about my past.
I didn't want to remember.
I did a truly terrible thing.
Exile in Naraku,
that was my punishment.
I hate it in Naraku.
The only thing I ever wanted was
to be just like everybody else.
This is for the best.
I can erase all my memories and
spend the rest of my life here.
Always watching Dream TV.
See? This isn't so bad.
Ker-chunk! Showtime!
J-JO Me-X TV.
L-live from Naraku.
H-Haneda is awful- oops,
I mean Haneda is awesome!
That the world may know peace.
That the world may know peace,
that the world may know peace.
That the world may know
peace, So that the world
may know peace!
Kobato.
This is the old church where we
met the priest who took us in
and cared for us when we
were kids. You remember?
A priest?
Yes, I remember.
The priest told the two of us
to never forget that phrase
because it would grant us the
kindness to forgive anything.
But my mother is-
she's somewhere else,
a place where she
can't forgive anymore.
What's this?
It's from the priest.
He asked me to hold onto it,
until you chose
to remember again.
A suicide?
But didn't I? I thought-
Her injuries healed.
But you know, I honestly
don't think that your mother
ever meant to stay here in this
world as long as she did.
So then.
Still.
That still doesn't
change what I did to her.
It's ok.
You were only trying to look
out for your little sister.
And if it hadn't been
for you, I might not have
ever made it as far
as I did, or at all!
Now, I have my very
own wings to guide me!
That the world may know peace.
I know that you can do it,
big brother.
You have the kindness to
forgive anything. So please.
Now's the time to
forgive yourself!
Hey Kobato!
Oh, hello Akira.
How's your morning? Let's
start heading to schoo-
Oh, this here's my big brother!
Hello there! You two go
to the same school?
U -uhh, yes! My name's
Akira, Akira Kikkawa!
Gotcha. Consider me a friend.
Oh, um, well why? I mean!
Yes! Kobato talks about you,
she says you're great!
It makes me so jealous,
I wish I could have an older
brother that was kind
and handsome just like you!
Wait. Seriously?
We better go, alright?
Sounds good. See you later!
Later on in the day, I -- I
mean, we -- made a decision.
Nothing too major, but I still
thought it was a good idea.
I wanted to tell all of
our friends everything.
If anyone deserved to know
the truth, it was them.
Lemme get this straight, a set
of hot twins wants to bang me?
I didn't say that!
I'm joking, sadly.
But that's a pretty messed-up
story you just told us .
I know it is.
Let's recap: You were caught
standing in front of a mirror
wearing Hiyoko's outfit spouting
kinky obscenities to yourself
and it weirded
the girls out, right?
Were you even
listening to me ?!
Don't worry kid, I get it.
So I guess you'll be seeking
some treatment now, huh?
Nah. I pretty much have
it under control,
so I think that I'm
going to hold off
until after graduation.
I see. Best of luck.
Thank you very much.
Studies show that more than
sixty percent of Japanese men
have excessive foreskin.
So never feel ashamed
of your body. Never.
What the hell do you think
I'm getting treatment for?!
Just thought I'd let
you know before you
make any rash decisions.
Thanks but no thanks!
And should you meet any female
medical professionals who have
difficulty performing their
duties due to insatiable
carnal desire,
tell me right away.
Someone make it stop!
You said you're
different on the inside,
but how can we
be sure about that?
Yeah, good point!
So, you mean, you still
have Shusuke's memories?
I remember everything,
it's all been consolidated.
You ruin parties,
and you suck at tests-
That'll be enough
outta you, jerkwad!
Sock it to him good!
Don't worry, you're way
below your quota!
Eeesh, it hurts twice as much
when there's just one of me!
I'm glad that's over with.
Hey, thanks for
all your help today.
So how about letting me talk
to Karura for a minute?
Uh, let's see. Your king
has returned once again!
That was weak.
Was it? Fear not,
my faithful subject.
I am here to lead you
into battle!
Pathetic.
That one too?
Just let me know
if Karura ever returns.
In the meantime, maybe
consider some acting classes.
So, are you done
working until you graduate?
Huh?
You're always welcome. We
can help keep an eye on you
at all times, ensuring
your youthful sex drive
is under control
during work hours.
And I thought I had problems?!
Well damn, so you're actually
crazier than I thought you were.
Speaking of, I think it's
time for me to close up shop
as a fixer.
Got other commitments.
Whatever you think is best.
Making good grades should
technically be your job.
Hit those books!
Right! Thank you for all the
support you've given me.
Never thought I'd live
to see Drac bow to me.
I might even shed a tear!
So, this is for you.
Go ahead, take it!
Huh? Um, but I'm done
doing contract work.
Now don't you go
giving me any lip, kid!
You may say that you're
Yoji Haneda, but who cares,
to me you'll always
be grumpy ol' Drac.
That is, unless you changed your
name and made up that story
in order to get off the hook
for everything you've owed me
since we've known
each other. Ya' got me?
Yup!
The truth is simple. Your
memory is unable to forget
this beautiful, sexy and sultry
body you want to ravage.
Woah there,
you've got it all wrong.
I'm not into young
children like that, ok?
Nope. You could barely control
little Drac. I remember.
Peeking below my dress
made you so happy!
Hey hey hey, put that skirt back
down you messed-up little kid!
Where are your parents?!
Who's looking after
this troubled youth?!
Someone take care of this cr-
Relax, hon.
Strange, today you're
acting a little different.
I mean, I always liked the
tough guy act, but this pure
and innocent getup is
equally hard to resist!
I can't wait
to unleash your inner ho.
Thanks, but for some reason, I
already feel terribly violated.
That's the idea.
Uh, I think I'll pass!
Uh, I'm sorry.
Ah, that's ok.
It's not surprising that
many can't wrap their heads
around the situation. It's
hard to explain, after all.
But it wouldn't be right
to keep secrets from them,
the very people who were
kind enough to accept us.
I probably could have gone
about telling them the truth
a little better in retrospect,
but at least
there's just one left.
Please forgive me- wha?
I think that I must have
accidentally bumped into you.
Good morning sir- mmph!
Are you alright?
I'm fine! Never
felt bett- mmph!
And you're sure
that you're doing ok?
Oh yes, I'm doing quite well
thank you, don't worry about it!
Come on now,
be honest with me.
An older woman once told me
that I should always do my best
to "fake it until I make it."
That's pretty clever!
I thought so. You should
definitely try it sometime.
Actually. I've already tried
faking it with my friends,
but it doesn't really work.
Is something wrong?
Kind of. I have to tell
someone something that's
both important
and a little weird.
Ah.
I don't know how they'll react,
so that's making me nervous.
Truth be told it's
a pretty pathetic story.
N-no, that's not
pathetic at all!
Hmm?
Because now and then everyone
runs into that same problem,
wanting to say something
with all your heart,
having trouble finding the
courage to do so. But you?
You'll find that courage,
I'm sure of it.
Thank you, miss,
miss whatever your name is.
Ohmigosh Ohmigosh Ohmigosh!
You figured yourself out!
That's seriously amazing!
Like putting together a
puzzle with a jillion pieces!
It's even harder than arching
your back like a rainbow!
How did your
spiritual pilgrimage go,
my timid little grasshopper?
How'd you find out about that?
Let's just say a certain
chicken let a few clucks
escape his beak.
Everything went well.
I can even tell you all about
little sister moé now
if you're still interested.
I've actually lost my
interest in that topic.
Huh? How come?
It was originally a competition
I had going with the chicken,
but he's into the "extreme."
Unlike him, I'm not quite
willing to pick at
"forbidden fruit." heh.
Don't tell me you mean-
Yeah, you guessed it
alright. Chicken is into-
Real little sister moé!
So, what are your future
plans? Anything special?
How 'bout a vacation?
The weather's great!
Perfect for the beach!
You like to swim?! I do!
I'm a freestyle phenom! My lung
capacity's like a whale's!
We could swim straight
across the world,
make a yearlong trip of it!
Ever built a snowman?!
Well now "Yukon" in Canada!
See I'm well-read too!
You won't even need
a tour guide when
you're with Miyako Yamashina,
a girl ripe with information!
I'm ripe in other
ways too, you know!
Um, I better get to class.
Your last manuscript
was well-received.
In most cases I'd have you
jump into the next one,
but with your situation
being what it is.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, well, let me know
when you're feeling ready
to work on another project.
You're a great writer.
At least I think so.
Thanks so much for everything.
Right. I'll be waiting!
Surprise!
Oh, hey. How are
you doing, Masako?
Is something wrong?
Why the long face?
What- Everything is just fine!
In fact my morale's about
to burst through the roof!
That's good. As long as
we're walking the same way,
wanna go to school together?
I would, but I've actually got
to go make a pretty important
phone call right now.
Really? Who do you
think you are,
some bigshot CEO?
I'm sorry, but I really
don't have time to waste
explaining it to you.
Well damn, I guess
you're being serious.
Gosh, you're so wound up.
It's actually kind of cute.
What the hell are
you talking about?
I'm not wound up! I'm just
really uncomfortable
around you?!
Right. You go ahead make that
call. I'll leave you alone now.
Till next time.
All right.
H-h-hello?! Morisato?!
Can you hear me?!
It's me, Yoji Haneda! Say
something if you're there!
Hey. Calm down, moron?
Sorry we haven't
talked in so long.
What's it been,
since freshman year?
Hayato and I actually saw
each other quite a bit.
Kakeru told me the news.
I'm not sure that I really
get it, but you've unified
or whatever it's called, right?
Yeah, that's exactly it!
I guess you really have
been a spectacular friend.
Not so fast.
I never wanted to
hang out with you, man.
I was just keepin' an eye out
'cause Kakeru asked me to.
How we started
out's not important.
You know how in manga the
guy and the girl who can't
stand each other get thrown
together into an adventure
and eventually become lovers?
We're kind of like that.
The hell?! That's
messed up. Seriously.
Look, I consider you to be
a very good friend, Kazuma.
And so, if you don't feel
the same way that I do.
I'll just double down
on my affections!
The way I feel about you will
be enough for the both of us,
it'll be perfect!
You're talkin' like a stalker!
Is that bad? I mean,
what's a stalker,
but someone who
really really loves you?
I get it! Enough! You know that
club, "Hetero"? Stop on by.
We'll talk, catch up some.
Mmm, sounds good!
By the way, there's one
more important thing
I need to tell you.
Huh? Lay it on me?
I don't know if
I should, actually.
What the hell, you can't
wuss out on me like that now.
All right.
That stupid long hair of yours
makes you look like a douche!
Yeah, says who?!
Says everybody!
I'm just telling you this
for your own good, man.
As your friend!
People all call you
that "long-hair-pretty-bo
oy-douc chey-guy"!
Sup dawg?
Good shit.
Hyah!
You oughta learn to
keep your mouth shut
and not piss me off, baldy.
Who you callin' baldy?!
It's you that oughta get
ready for an ass-whupping.
Let's go get him, boys!
How in the-
Yanagihara.
Flame.
Birdes.
Yeah!
Eeesh, you have
got to be kidding me!
Huh?
Guess I'll see ya around!
Wha.
Wait up, guys!
Thank you, Kazuma.
My friendship with you
ultimately led me to her.
Hey. Who was that girl?
When I turned around,
there she was!
Well then, who might this be?
Allow me to introduce
myself. I am Yoji Haneda.
Would you mind not further
complicating the image
I have of Takashi?!
My mistake, I'll never
do it again. Uh.
'Kay, get ready!
"This just about brings
an end to our regularly
scheduled program. Please join
us again in the future."
Or something else that's meant
to wring some waterworks
out of you.
Just cry a little bit, ok?
Enough of that, though,
how are my listeners doing?
Believe it or not,
the Condor lives!
Surely everyone remembers
my tragically heroic death
in episode eight! But
appearances can be deceiving,
as true legends like the Condor
are not limited by mere notions
of life and death! Still, I
appreciate all of your fan mail
and "Condor-lences,"
and appreciate those who
just chuckled at my adlib.
Improv isn't easy!
And now I leave you with this
final nugget of wisdom--
an egg of wisdom, rather.
Fry it, scramble it, boil it,
but whatever you do,
take it to heart!
Really, the yolk's
healthier than you think!
Are you listening? Here goes:
Don't be afraid to turn
the channel in life.
Sure, the radio or TV may come
with presets, and you may find
yourself compelled to keep
the dial centered on what's
already there for you,
but don't sell yourself short!
The direction of your
life is dependent
on the channel you choose.
If you don't like that channel,
then change it. Easy!
Easier said
than done, you say?!
Come on, I came back
from the dead!
If I can self-resurrect,
then you've got no excuses
for not flipping a knob!
The world's a huge,
exciting place;
no two channels are alike.
So sit yourself down in
that metaphorical sofa
and get to channel surfing!
Don't let those bullies
and doubters hog the remote!
You control your destiny!
Get rid of that inner
Naraku! And you thought
I wouldn't bring
this back full circle!
Pah, Condor's a professional!
That's right, if you learn
anything from this story,
please learn that you
control yourself.
Also learn that the
Condor can't be destroyed.
Invincible, I tell
you! Invincible!
I kid, that's secondary.
Sort of. Don't get in a rut,
be true to yourself,
and you'll do just fine.
People were not meant
to live a lonely life.
Remember that, and be
reassured that your brethren
are always there at your side.
We are not angels, and we
cannot soar through the sky.
Even so, that does not mean we
cannot at least flap our wings.
I'm positive that if
you all join together,
your life on this Earth can be
enjoyable. I'm certain of it.
After all, it would seem that
not all of us are without wings.
Hey, you made it! Thanks for
sticking with me for so long.
Our story's more or less over.
Well, that's not entirely true;
it's technically
still going on,
but we just don't have enough
time to go over everything.
Long story short, we all
started living life with
an eye towards the future.
Oh! You might find this
kind of interesting, in my
studies I found out that people
like you are what experts
call "Inner Self Helpers",
or I-S-H for short.
They basically take people who
have fallen apart, like us,
and help piece
them back together,
granting some
much-needed relief.
We couldn't have
done it without you.
So, on behalf of all of us,
I thank you. Keep it up!
What's the deal, do we start
going to the same school today?
No, silly! I just need to go
so I can fill your teachers
and guidance counselor
in on your situation.
Surprise!
Come on. Bring out Takashi!
But, I can't!
Guess I'll have
to slug you first!
Don't you think it's
a little too early
to be acting so violently!
Aw, aren't you just adorable.
I wish I had a little sister
as cute as you. But that doesn't
mean I'm eager to marry
into the family or anything!
Oh. I think. If I had an older
sister that was just like you.
I'd never be sad again!
Oh my gosh, she is so precious.
You think so, huh?
I'll follow you to
the ends of the Earth!
I spotted you conversating
from a distance and it looked
much too interesting to pass up!
So I hightailed it over here
fast as I could, good
thing these tires were
built for speed!
Am I too late?
No matter, I'll just
start a new subject!
So Kakeru and I had some
stew yesterday for lunch.
Come to think of it, can
you still smell the garlic
on my breath?
Maybe if I get my lips
close enough to your nose
and breathe out, the spirit
of Drac will take over!
Guess I might as well try it.
No ya' don't!
Apparently there's some demand
for me to put out another book.
Do you mind if I ask
you for some advice?
If it weren't for Shusuke's
article on 88th Birthday,
people might not have ever
given it another chance.
So, thank you.
Huh?
How direct can you get?!
Care to have another whiff?
Back of the line, sister!
C,mon, were going to be late.