JO Me-X TV.
Bringing you
seven trillion channels.
This is A.C.T
Naraku Central Television.
JO Me-X TV.
Bringing you
seven trillion channels.
This is A.C.T.
Naraku Central Television.
Geez, Birdy, I'm gonna
be late again 'cause
you didn't wake me up on time!
Sorry, I'm not the perfect
little sister who does
all the chores and
takes care of you too.
I guess I'm more
like a cousin, huh?
Surprise! Good morning!
Did you sleep well,
future hubby?
Um, Asuka. What are you doing?
Sharing a little
affection with my man.
You're making a scene!
Who cares?!
Let's give 'em an eyeful!
Hey, let go of him!
Listen, future
sister-in-law, he's mine,
so I get to manhandle him.
No need to get
all jealous n'stuff.
I mean, not unless-
Oh my! That's so wrong.
It's not wrong!
He's mine!
And we're always
going to be together!
Forever!
Wait a second.
What's that mean.
Oh, no!
Make way, everyone!
My brakes aren't
working so great!
Oh, hello, I didn't
see you standing there;
what a surprise, we just seem
to keep running into each other
everywhere, huh?
It must be like
fate or something.
Call me old-fashioned,
but this feels like something
straight out of a fairytale,
wouldn't you agree?
Like when a prince
and princess are destined
to share a sweet kiss?
Hey!
Take my advice. When it
comes to those girls,
it's like that song by Freaky
Five. Laugh all of them off
with extreme genocide, 'kay?
The only girl that
you need in your life is me.
Today, once again,
nothing in the world is wrong.
Yeah, right.
"Everyone in the world likes me,
and all arrows point to me, too.
Wouldn't it be nice if
a world like that existed?"
Well, that's how our story
begins tonight on DJ Condor's.
"Love Letters From the Abyss!"
As always, this program
is brought to you by
the host with the most,
the Ayatollah of rock'n rolla,
the man, the myth,
the legend-DJ Condor!
For those of you tuning in,
boy do we have a doozy
for you tonight!
It's a story of deception,
alternate realms, sexy babes,
and a whole lot more!
It's a real whale of a tale!
You'd better strap yourselves
in, kiddos, because trust me,
this is gonna be
one bumpy ride!
Hey, nice to meet you!
How are you doing today?
If it's okay,
I'm gonna be counting on you
for a little while,
that is, if you'd be so kind!
This is Shusuke Chitose.
He styles himself
as a real ladies' man,
but he's always broke,
even though he works
various part-time jobs.
And this is Alexander,
a restaurant in Yanagihara.
Pay attention.
Because this place is the focal
point, and it all begins here!
Oh, hey, hot stuff,
didja miss me?!
Just zip it.
Okay?
I wanna have a singles' party.
Oh, yeah?
That's a great idea!
Wow, you da man, Karuo!
You never cease
to amaze me, dude!
Did I ever tell you that
I really look up to you
and that I think
you're a genius and stuff?!
I really hope my butt-kissing-
I mean, admiration-
means that I'm invited
to this party!
Yeah, don't worry, you are!
This scruffy, yet handsome guy
dreaming up the singles' party
is Alexander's owner,
Karuo Karube.
Age 35.
A lifelong bachelor
and a bit of a perv.
In addition to chicks, he has
a thing for group urination.
What we need are chicks.
Kakeru, I'm leaving it up to
you to round up some hot ones.
And also, make sure they're the
kind of girls that get scared
when it thunders and
need a big, strong man
to console them, 'kay?
Forget it.
What?!
This is Kakeru Otori.
Stylish, cool, and handsome.
A bit of a playboy, and
because of his connections,
our source to find hot chicks.
But since it sounds like he's
refusing to help us procure
said hot chicks for the party-
Crap!
This party is doomed!
We won't get girls that get
scared by thunder and need big,
strong men to console them!
Then why not just change
the requirements to girls
who walk barefoot on the
beach and stare pensively
under storm-tossed skies?!
Excellent idea!
I can envision girls
like the kind you see
in perfume commercials that
don't make a lick of sense,
or maybe like
actresses in any number
of pretentious
art-house movies!
Alright then.
We need you.
How 'bout it?
We're counting on you, dude!
Give it up.
Stop closing the door!
Come on, Kakeru, why do
you have to be like that?
Without your help, do you know
what our chick selection
is limited to?
Cougars that stick tips in
my pants and that toothless,
homeless broad in the alley.
Tell them all that
I said hi, would you?
Kakeru, we're begging you here!
You've got a network of hot
chicks that me and Karuo don't!
Can't you throw a few our way?!
Won't you please find it
in your heart to help those
who are less
fortunate than you?!
I'm sure you'll
manage somehow, Shu.
Alright, fine!
Thanks to you, me and Karuo
won't be getting any,
Mr. Selfish!
That's a good thing, especially
since Karuo is engaged.
Wait, you're getting hitched?!
Yeah, next month in fact.
He's also gonna be a daddy.
And you, knocked her up?!
That's yes to both, and
that's exactly why I wanna have
a singles' party before
I have to settle down!
That's so cool!
One last fling in the face
of a looming domestic life
with the same woman!
You're going out
like a real champ, dude!
I hope you bang
a bunch of broads
to commemorate the occasion!
That's not a good idea,
unless you want to get
more girls pregnant
than just your fiancée.
Hey, this party's a
get-together, not an orgy
where we do the
horizontal mambo all night!
The only thing we're gonna
be trading is conversations,
not condoms, you understand?!
Heh, I've never heard
of "trading condoms" before.
Wow, So how's that work exactly?
You pass 'em around before
or after you use 'em?
You misunderstand, smartass!
Besides, I don't use rubbers!
A real man never does!
Which explains why
your fiancée is pregnant.
Hey, flunkie,
can I get a refill?
Right away, sir!
Sorry, I didn't see
you were empty.
Here you go.
As for that nickname, I may not
be a "flunkie" for much longer.
That's right!
Kinako here's
gonna attempt to pass
the college
entrance exams again!
And if she aces them, she'll
go to school with sexy coeds
who run around the dorms
in their underwear
and shower together!
Well, I don't know about
that, but I am hoping that
the third time's the charm for
me taking the entrance exams.
They're really hard,
so I'm really going to have
to buckle down and study
for the entire next month.
I'm taking the next four weeks
off to do that, so wish me luck.
I'm so gonna miss
seeing you in your uniform!
Aw, thank you, Shusuke.
That's super sweet.
You know, I think
I'm gonna miss this place.
Likewise, and that's
why we wanna throw you
a going away party.
We were just talking
about that, in fact.
Right, Shusuke?
Yeah, we sure were!
What better way to say goodbye
than a kickass party?!
Oh, man, Karuo is a genius!
That's nice, but no.
Don't go through
the trouble just for me.
It's no trouble
at all, we insist!
Just bring yourself and
a couple of hot friends,
and it'll be a killer singles'
- I mean - send-off party
you will never forget!
And there's this one:
Kinako Mochizuki.
Cute-as-a-button part-time
waitress and frequent recipient
of Karuo's sexual harassment.
Every year at this time, she
takes a vacation and uses it
to study for the
college entrance exams.
Unfortunately, she's flunked
them two years in a row now,
but as she said,
she's trying again.
You're okay with a waitress?
What happened to girls that need
consoling when it thunders,
or ones that stare pensively
under stormy skies?
If you're not gonna
help us plan the party,
butt out, wise guy!
Are you really sure
about doing this, Boss?
Yeah, I insist!
We'll reserve the bar for your
private going-away party
tomorrow night.
How does eight o'clock
sound, Kinako?
You can make it then, right?
Yeah, sure.
Again, this is really kind of
you, and drinks with you guys
should be lots of fun!
It sure will!
And, maybe, who knows?!
As much as I like you
in that outfit,
perhaps I'll get lucky tomorrow
night and see you out of it!
Um, Kinako, I was
just joking; are you mad?
No not at all, peaceout! Well,
I've gotta get back to work now.
One chick down .
I know.
But she didn't say anything
about bringing any hot friends,
did she?
Kakeru!
That's my cue to leave.
Wanna stay here with
the loudmouth or go with me?
No, don't!
Stay here, Kakeru!
But you can leave, Shusuke.
You've been nursing
that cup of coffee forever.
Hey!
Karuo!
Did you hear what your
employee just said to me?!
She's insinuating that I'm cheap
because all I bought was coffee!
But you didn't.
That coffee was on the house.
This is Eriko Hino,
a student at a girl's college,
and the so-called
"platoon leader"
of Alexander's waitstaff.
Nice to look at,
but she's not nice to me.
So?
What do we do, Shusuke?
Well, Kinako
can't be the only girl,
we've gotta get
some more chicks.
But we should really try
to invite some nice ones.
No mean-as-hell
ball-busters like Eriko, 'kay?
Idiot.
Didn't you notice the
"mean-as-hell ball-buster"
was still here?
Well?
No, hold on, I meant like your
"sweet-as-pie", "head server!"
Uh-huh!
Leave him alone, Eriko, please?
Come on, he's making way
too much racket in here.
Of course I'll leave him alone;
you know I'm always happy
to do anything you
ask of me, Kakeru!
So, what was all this business
I heard about a party?
Um, well, I hope you don't
mind me asking you this, Eriko.
But what do you do
when you hear the crack
of thunder in the sky?
Huh?
Thunder?
Are you mental?
No.
Look, you're a girl,
so when the sky goes "BOOM!",
do you maybe fall to your knees
and go "Eeeek?!" Like that?
You are mental!
Girls like that
don't really exist!
They do!
They're out there
somewhere, I know!
And I'm gonna find those
girls and they're gonna come
to the killer party we're
about to have, you'll see!
I hope you have a time machine,
'cause the only place
you'll find women
like that is in the past!
Eriko's out.
Thank you.
Huh? What gives?
All I did was ask about this
party and you never answered me.
They're having a singles'
party tomorrow night.
Yeah?
I'm there!
Wow!
I love a good party!
That was easy.
Of course it was.
Haven't you ever heard
what my friends call me?
Ask anyone, and they'll tell you
that I didn't earn the nickname
"Eri the Party Monster"
for nothing!
You must be proud.
Who's showing up to this thing?
Doctors?
Lawyers?
Celebs?
A restaurateur with sex appeal.
A broke guy looking to score.
Plus Kinako and
at least one escort.
Hang on.
Um, I'm washing
my hair tomorrow night.
But you're the "Party Monster!"
No, not if you and the boss
are the only guys coming.
If Kakeru came,
I might change my mind.
You "might?",So if
I did agree to come,
you still wouldn't be sure?
Wow, You stuck-up bitch.
Ohhh!
I just love it when you
talk dirty to me, Kakeru!
Tell me what a bad,
nasty girl I've been!
That's two chicks now!
We just need one more!
Yeah, but who?!
Hey, wait, I got it!
How 'bout we order
one of those naughty nurses?!
That'll make three!
Where and when's
this party tomorrow?
Here at the bar, eight o'clock.
I'll have it reserved
exclusively for the party.
I haven't been to
a party in a long time.
Alright, I can't wait.
Um, Eriko, you stopped getting
invited to parties because
you got totally plastered
and ended up trashing 'em?
Oh, how sweet!
I'm touched that you know
so much about me, Kakeru!
Yep, she's definitely in!
So, you really don't care
who comes to your party?
Nope, not as long as she is
a real chick and has a pulse.
Well, I guess the two waitresses
meet those exacting standards,
don't they?
You're coming to the party.
Aren't you?
Count me out.
I'd just be a third wheel
since you have two girls.
Don't worry about it.
I've got someone in mind
to be our third girl.
There ya' go!
Thanks, but don't put
yourselves out for me.
It's okay, dude;
the more the merrier, right?
Uh.
I think that including
me would end up making
the mood less merry, don't you?
No, that's why we need you.
That icy demeanor of yours, it
gives our trio a little variety.
Alright, fine, I'll go.
Booyah!
Now we've got Kakeru, too.
I've got something to do, guys,
so I'll see you two tomorrow.
Yeah, Sure.
So what'd you think about this?
It was good.
Nice job there, Shu.
This should
take care of my tab.
I guess they're
looking for help,
because Kinako's
leaving for a month.
'Kay.
That'll be a carbonara and
a blended coffee, right?
What are you doing?!
That's not the right way to
get your waitress' attention!
Wait, these things
aren't striped.
Unstriped panties
are the worst.
Um, sorry.
But that's what I wear.
I hate unstriped panties,
so not anymore, you don't!
Let go of me!
Even a good tip isn't worth
this kind of humiliation!
Stop it, you little pervert!
Wow.
There's never
a dull moment at Alexander.
I love this place.
Yanagihara runs a great
distance east and west,
with the station serving
as the border between them.
The west side houses the city's
booming business district,
while the east is home to
the entertainment district,
which is a really
bustling place at night.
And a spot where we now
find one of our major players.
Here, look.
Hayato Narita.
About twenty years old.
Does odd jobs but
is technically unemployed.
Zodiac sign and
blood type are both secret.
A hard-boiled guy; well,
at least by his own description.
For real?
Yes,I always thought
testicles were something
that only an octopus had.
There he is.
Hey, Drac.
Help a "sustah" out and
buy something, would ya?
These ain't my thing.
Yeah, right.
More like 'cause
yo ass has no money.
That is incorrect,
not because of that.
It's not his ass that has
no money, but Drac himself
who has no money.
Am I right?
Wow, You still haven't picked up
the local lingo yet, huh?
You gotta work on your street
slang, don't be so literal.
I am not so little.
And I know I may be poor, but
at least I earn my own keep,
on the other hand,
I bet you probably get
some form of allowance,
but you don't really earn
a single cent of it,
do you, Alice?
Am I right, Little Miss
New-To-This-Country?
Uh, sorry.
I no speakee
your language, sir.
No shit!
That's your problem!
Give Miss Thang a break.
Go easy on her, would ya, Drac?
Come on, remember,
she's only a kid.
Yeah, that's exactly why I'm
tryin' to get her to learn.
She's gotta be streetsmart
like me, this ain't no place
for a kid who probably still
wears bear-print panties.
I am insulted, Drac!
Mine have no bears!
They're sexy,
thrilling and lacy!
Take a look!
Madre de Dios, sweet thang!
Pull your dress down, girl!
You can't be flashin'
all your bidness out here
on the street like that!
The reason is, I am a child.
Adults, you see, they do not
find children attractive.
Not at all.
Wrong, honey!
The men in this country are
full-on "fuh-reaks" for kids
and for people
who dress like them!
C'mon, man!
That's just a bad
stereotype of Japanese men
that you're helpin' perpetuate!
Do you want to do it, Drac?
With me?
Do what?
You have one, right?
One of those "peninsula"
things men have in their pants?
So do you want to take it, and
then, um, well, how do you say?
Get "biz-zay" and knock shoes?
Well, Come on,
come on, come on!
No!
Now learn the language,
and watch out for
dirty old men out here.
There's a lot of them.
"Dirty?" Do they
all need baths?
Should I offer to bathe them?
No!
And that's not what I meant!
Go hit those
language books now!
Hey!
Drac!
Over here!
Huh?
What?
For you.
What's this about?
Do you always have to be
such a pain in the butt?
Come on, answer it, Look,
he told me if you came here,
he really wanted
to talk to you.
"He?" Who do you mean?
It's Eiji.
Hey!
What the hell, Drac?!
I try to help get you a job and
that's how you respond to it?!
Ingrate!
Thanks, but the job was crap,
and probably illegal, too,
if Eiji's involved.
Speakin' of jobs, are there any
available here at Pal Crepe?
What?
For you?
Yep.
If there are, Harue.
Simply stop by the
Narita Contractor's Office
in your neighborhood.
I'm sorry!
We don't currently have
any openings at this time.
Asshole.
And, since you need employment.
Might I suggest this
job for Eiji that you
just stupidly turned down?!
I told you, I don't like
Eiji's jobs; they're sketchy!
Like squattin' in
condemned-lookin' apartments
for a week.
You should see the
rats in those places!
Sometimes his jobs entail
havin' to take really
suspicious-lookin'
packages and leave them
in lockers at the station.
Even worse, sometimes
I have to bury stuff
out in the middle of nowhere.
Yeah, so what?
What kind of person
begs for a job, gets it,
then complains
about it afterwards?
Eiji paid you for all of those
jobs you did, didn't he?
So then what the hell
are you whining about?
I help people, and Eiji's
jobs cause more problems
for people who're
already in trouble.
I didn't know the
Narita Contractor's Office
was in a position
to pick and choose.
Sadly, it's not,
I want honest work.
Don't you have
anything like that for me?
Come on, anything at all.
Huh?
If you want some honest work,
then wash the truck for me,
okay?
Sure, but so you know, the
Narita Contractor's Office
charges nine-fifty an hour.
Oh, please, come on, Narita.
It's honest work.
Don't you know that some
of the most honest work
is the unpaid kind?
Well, that's the kind
I don't do, see ya'.
Help out a friend.
Think of it like morality:
you'd loan an umbrella
to an old man who was
in need of one, wouldn't you?
Sure, if he paid me or offered
me somethin' in return,
like maybe somethin' to eat?
Fine!
I get it!
You drive a hard bargain, jerk!
You can have one
crepe on the house,
but only after you're done!
You're payin' me in food?
Geez.
While we're on that subject.
You never paid me
for your ramen last week.
So unless you want to do
so right now, get scrubbing!
Right away.
So I ended up workin'
Eiji's job after all,
I've gotta get somethin'
else better and soon.
At least I hope I can.
Maybe a good job's
not in the cards.
What are you looking at?
The place I'll have
to return to one day, my home.
Oh, that's some
imagination you've got there.
Asuka!
Sorry, those are my friends.
See ya!
That place is real.
So are my feelings for you.
He's real cute, huh?
Asuka Watarai, I love you.
I have to finish things
quickly, I don't have
much time left here.
I am not of this world.
I transferred here
from Gretagard,
a world beyond the skies.
The real me is a candidate
to be Gretagard's next king.
One of the "Four Feathers
of 10,000 Colors".
The sacred knight, Hawk.
The sky goes ever onward,
unbroken, right?
This is just an example,
but-What we're telling you
is that simple kind
of a fairytale.
We got this from a caller
named Mr. Number One,
and he wants to know if there'll
be more forced panty shots
in the next episode.
The answer is yes,
Mr. Number One,
both next time, and all
the times after that!
See you next panties -
I mean - episode!