It sounded like a gunshot,
and when I turned around-
What do you think happened?
Some black dude got shot!
Alice.
Alice!
Drac!
Are you all right?
Bullets.
They shoot Mr. Marty!
Martinez?!
Who was it?!
I don't know him.
He wear a hat on the head.
Who would?
A hat.
A man in a hat.
The hat man, he said-
I will kill Narita.
Son of a bitch!
There's no reason
to worry, the doctors said
he's gonna be just fine.
He's lucky that the bullet
didn't hit any organs.
He can check out of
the hospital in a few days.
I see.
And?
That's all you've got to say?
Jeez, Drac.
I thought you were
gonna blow a gasket earlier.
Yes.
In his belly, Drac had
very much firewood burning.
Firewood nothin'.
You couldn't see me anyway,
wench, you were too busy cryin'
your damn eyes out.
You are wrong, I cried none.
I am a cool keeper cutie!
Uh.
What the hell kinda'
language are you speaking?
Enunciate!
Ow!
Don't pinfh, Miffer Drac!
Or no strif
rock-pafer-scissors!
Take it.
That'll teach ya' to lie!
Fine then, horse
around all you want.
The fact still remains that some
armed lunatic is on the loose,
running rampant in our city.
So for the time being,
don't stay out as late as usual.
Understood?
Yes, I understood
you clear and loud.
That goes for you too, Drac.
Huh?
What do I have
to worry ab-I hear ya.
Interesting, so the guy in
the hat is R-Wing's Archbishop.
Yeah.
And what's more, I doubt
this'll affect just you and me.
If we're not careful,
Takashi and Kobato
could be in trouble, too.
You think so?
That doesn't sound good!
We should've turned that
damn fruitcake in to the cops
when we had the chance!
That's enough,
Hayato, take it easy.
For now, let's just help
Takashi and the others, OK?
All right.
I'm being serious.
No running off and
making rash decisions...
Remember "That the world
may know peace", got me?
Don't worry.
I made the old man a promise
I'm not gonna break.
Hey Karou, I think it's about
time to throw out all this smut.
"Smut?" Don't you mean "trash?"
Watch what you say,
'cause not all smut is trash!
Be a little more sensitive
with your vocabulary usage.
Damn kids these days, back in my
time, you'd dive into a river
just to fetch a porno mag
floating downstream!
Anyway, I'm taking this out.
Anyone out there?
--Guess not.
--Chitose?
I-is that you, Hiyoko?
Uh. Hello.
This is a surprise!
So what brings you here today?
I thought this was the day
that you usually take off.
Well- I just wanted
to check on your injury.
Injury? Oh, right, the injury!
It's fine,
I've got a thick skull!
Why do you ask?
So, Let me get this straight.
You're actually
worrying about me?
Yeah, don't flatter yourself!
It's just that you
got hurt protecting me.
And I feel
somewhat responsible.
So please, let me
help clean you up.
Hold still for me, please.
Uh- no problem.
Looks like the wound
still hasn't closed up.
I'll start off
by disinfecting the area.
Is this hurting you?
No, uh!
Go right ahead.
Try not to move around, k?
Whatever you say.
I don't know if I can take it!
Oh God!
D-did I hurt you?
Sorry about that.
It's so moist and
sensitive right now.
"Moist and sensitive"!
Don't worry, I'll rub it
gently this time.
"Gently rubbing!"
I-is everything all right?
Um, yes!
Everything's peachy.
Looks like Karuo's influence
is rubbing off on me.
That's right, accept it!
Smut, trash, whatever,
you love it all!
Get ready,
I'm gonna keep going.
Oh n-no!
It's too much!
I'm all done now,
sorry it took so long.
Go ahead and sit up.
Wha?
Oh, right, gotcha.
The wrapping job's
kind of shoddy.
I guess I'm no doctor.
Nonsense,
thanks for the help!
You have truly moved me.
I think I might cry!
Well, it wasn't
that big of a deal.
What a modest caretaker!
This gauze, infused
with your incomparable TLC,
will no doubt protect me
from microscopic bacteria,
but also from
life's daily challenges!
Such a sweet gesture!
Don't exaggerate like that.
I'll treasure this day forever!
It's like I was meant
to get smacked in the head!
Hiyoko's love gauze
will never come off!
She who giveth,
can taketh away!
What are you doin' here?
I just got done
snacking over at Pal Crepe.
Next time,
you oughta come with!
Yum yum!
We're nowhere near
Pal Crepe right now.
Right, it's pretty far
come to think of it,
but when I saw you walking by,
I thought I'd surprise you
and follow your every footstep!
Of course.
Don't tell me
you're upset with me.
Wait, are you?
Do I really
embarrass you that much?
Oh please don't
start yelling obscenities!
Nah, there's more important
stuff goin' on tonight.
Is that so?
What kind of important stuff?
None of your business.
Let's go.
Hey, wait a minute!
Why're you so
forceful all of a sudden?
No questions, look,
just don't let go of my hand
till I say so, got it?
Hayato, is everything ok?
You're acting
a little different.
From now on
I'm gonna be protectin' ya.
Whoopee!
Atta girl, that's it.
Mew?
Head straight home.
And don't come back to
Yanagihara for a little while,
I'll let you know
when it's ok, ya' got it?
The streets have become a bit
more dangerous than usual.
Some crazy bastard's been
runnin' around town with a gun.
Our bicycle hunt's gonna
have to be shelved for now,
just wait at home until
I can figure everything out.
Yes sir!
Don't worry about
anything coming between us,
for absence makes
the heart grow fonder!
Well, she looked
like she was listening.
Least I hope.
Why hello, Hayato!
What brings you
to this classy joint?
Lemme guess, you're an
angry thug lookin' to score!
Ooh, it's so hot in here!
I'm so wet and sticky!
I see you peeking!
How 'bout we go back to
your place for some fun-
Stop while you're ahead, wench,
or you'll end up
embarrassin' the both
of us; you got any idea
where Otori
might be hangin' out?
Um, you mean Kakeru?
I've heard that he's
always chillin' at this place.
I'd like to see him.
Well, yeah, he's definitely
here, but if I were you,
I wouldn't-
Wouldn't what?
Eh, never mind about that.
Come with me!
Otori?
How ya doin' there, buddy?
Uh, are you drinkin'?
What the hell's all that stuff?
Yep, I'm drunk!
Drunk and sick!
Living in this world always
puts me in a drinkin' mood!
Earth to Chicken,
come in, Chicken!
Cock-a-doodle-doo, and all of
that other damn chicken stuff.
Knock it off, Shu.
Oh, it's you, Hayato.
Make up your mind already;
surely, it takes more than
one drink to make you change.
I thought some people
didn't even need alcohol
to transform into
someone else, am I right?
Shut up.
Still, I can't say that I ever
expected Hayato to come here,
though I was kinda
hoping at some point
we'd cross paths again.
I'm a little embarrassed,
letting you see me
in this state, drunk
and 'under the weather'.
But what's done is done.
Allow me to reintroduce myself!
My name is Kakeru Otori, and I'm
a big boy, seventeen years old!
Whatever, weirdo.
Listen up, the only
reason I came here
is to give you a warning.
Oh?
Enlighten me.
The nut case you
fought with from R-Wing,
that Archbishop guy?
You're gonna have
to watch out for that dude.
He's on a rampage and goin'
after just about everybody.
How 'bout that?!
So he caused quite a ruckus
at Alexander, I take it.
How'd you hear about that?
I have my connections.
Then how about you start takin'
this a little more seriously.
That psycopath is
still out there, dammit.
How sad, I think you're
underestimating my abilities
to handle myself,
plus he'd have to deal with me
and my faithful Flame Birdes!
It's not you that I'm
actually worried about, look,
everyone around you
is also in danger.
How Tragic.
One of my buddies
was shot last night.
That's your reaction?
Let me spell it out
nice an' clear for ya.
Your family needs
to be protected.
And that includes Naru,
you hear me?!
Naru?
Naru.
That's right!
Used ta call her sister!
Yeah, she means
nothing to me nowadays.
You bastard!
Piece of shit.
You may change how you look,
but you're still dumbass Otori.
You're on your own, good luck.
What a disappointment,
I was hoping that you'd
eventually get in the mood
to have some real fun.
Shut up, this whole thing
was a waste of my time.
In the future, I'm not gonna
even give you a warning.
Sorry to bother you.
Hey, let's plan on
meeting again sometime soon.
'Cept next time, why don't we
talk about our relationship.
Your manuscript has
been received, thanks!
Now before I forget, that Tamaki
Hosokawa story I'm waiting on,
is that review coming
along nicely for you?
Yep, I'm almost
through with it!
Should be done by next week.
Regarding that, I got
a little curious and thought
I would do some "independent
research" of my own.
She has two books
out now, right?
"Smiling Inside"
and "88th Birthday."
I forget, which one
are you writing about again?
This one here.
Ah, I wasn't
expecting that; you read it?
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
Is there something wrong?
Well, I haven't quite
read it myself just yet,
but a colleague did mention
that the ending to this one
is pretty depressing,
at least more downbeat
than "Smiling Inside." Thought
you might want to know.
Yeah, I 've heard rumors.
She probably tried to
set it completely apart
from her first work.
It's the same mistake a lot
of young authors make.
They have one big seller, and
after that the expectations
are just too high to handle.
They try to mature and evolve
so they won't get pigeonholed,
but in the end they're
left with a confused
and disappointed audience.
Sophomore efforts can
really make or break careers.
Unfortunate, don'cha think?
It sure is.
Yep, everyone involved gets
the short end of the stick.
The print company,
bookstores, customers,
not to mention
your humble editor.
Is what you said true?
That my book, you thought
it was interesting.
Those words made me very happy.
Sounds pretty
disheartening to me.
So you get it now?
If you were to write one of
your trademark glowing reviews
for that girl, the ones you're
so good at, then it's bound
to do wonders
for her book sales.
And that can only
be a good thing, right?
That's perfect!
Yet another fantastic, idea!
You're quite enthusiastic, too
bad you already bought a copy,
I could've just given you one!
Never mind that,
you're already paying me
to write a glowing review.
Plus, doesn't my buying the book
make money for your company?
Maybe, but it won't do
a bit of good for me!
We could sell a billion
copies and I still wouldn't
get a promotion or a raise
from the suits up top!
Yep, I'll be a mid-level
editor all my life!
Well, you just
keep up the good work!
Where am I?
What the-?
Nothing unusual on my end.
Take care!
Where's the damn sugar?!
Crap is bitter as hell.
Hey there, kid.
Um, hello, Mr. Narita, right?
Yeah.
It-it's been so long!
I guess it has.
But I'm curious, what
exactly are ya doin' here?
Just some shopping.
For now I think ya'd
be better off stickin' to
your local stores,
this area's gotten
kinda dangerous recently.
Trust me on this one.
I bought bread!
I saw a commercial
for this bakery,
and the food looked delicious.
Long story short, he wanted
to try some of it out
and sent me on a mission, so-
So ya ended up comin'
all the way out here?
But the line was long
and the bakery was so busy,
I didn't even get my
order till it got dark.
Why do ya even like bread?
You're Japanese, wench,
ya oughta be eatin' rice!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Don't worry 'bout it.
Next time just let me know, OK?
Then I can get it for ya.
Oh.
OK, well then, thank you so
very much for your kindness!
Now go straight home,
with no other stops.
Ya got it?
Yes.
Also, Mr. Narita?
What is it? Yeah?
Sometime, please stop by the
house and I'll cook dinner
for all of us!
My way of saying thank you!
Absolutely.
Guess I'll be seein' ya'.
There's gotta be some place
I haven't looked yet.
Meow!
Cut it out!
Meow meowww!
"Meow" my foot,
ya damn mental case!
Did anything I said
yesterday get through
that thick skull of yours?!
And what the hell's up with
this idiotic cat wench costume
you've been pesterin' me in?!
It's always breakin'
my concentration, damn it!
Nyo nyo nyo!
I did exactly as you asked!
So strong, those words
that escaped your lips
on that fateful day.
My precious Naru,
I must apologize for
misleading you so,
for tonight I'm not
wearing my work clothes.
It's unfair for you to see
me in anything other than
my manly work attire.
Come tomorrow evening,
I will appear before you,
dressed in work clothes rich
with the scent of perspiration
you know and love.
Those were your words!
But yet again you
torment me with casual wear.
OK.
So!
Until you come around,
I'll flaunt my feminine,
feline charms to
"purr-fection"!
Come to think of it,
I've always been more
of a dog person.
So funny and diligent!
Uh, scuse me?
I'm so thankful you volunteered
to help me look for my bicycle,
and that even now
you're still searching.
You're going to
all those places tonight?
Huh?
Hold on a second!
I'm just plannin'
a grocery route!
Don't jump to
stupid conclusions.
There's no need to be
so modest with me!
I already know what
a sweet person you are,
not to mention that you're
a fan of the barely legal look!
I've known some crazy wenches,
but you've gotta be
the craziest wench I know!
I've finally
found you, Narita!
Oh, great.
If I remember correctly,
that gun doesn't have
any more ammo in it.
You're gonna regret
what you've done to me,
gonna regret it real soon!
I've been through hell
and back to get here!
You reap what you sow,
I suppose.
Chew on this!
Bastard!
This time you
won't be so lucky!
Cut it out!
That's it!
No one makes
a fool outta me!
Get mad!
Be quiet!
Everyone will face the
barrel of my vengeance!
You hear that?
Punish him!
No, I can't.
Damn it all!
You're gonna pay!
Mess him up!
He'll regret it!
Just shut up!
You ready to meet your maker?!
Show no mercy to your enemy!
Stop, stop, stop!
Anger!
Enough!
Punish him!
Shut up!
Ain't so tough when there's
a gun in your face, are ya?!
What are you waiting for?!
--Kill him!
--I told you to shut up!
Are you ready to change?
Let's do it!
Shit!
That the world may know peace,
that the world may know peace,
Hayato?
Um-
That the world may know peace,
that the world may know-
What the hell?
The YFB?
Guess Chicken cares about
his sister more than he lets on.
You look tired.
Let's get something to eat
or just go to the club, 'kay?
Go ahead and rest up a bit.
But first, why don't we
finally have that conversation
about just the two of us?
Hey man, don't go
dozing off just yet.
Hayato?
Hey there Phoenix.
It's been quite a while,
hasn't it?
You still keeping
all your wits about you?
It can't be; you're not-
Oh, but I am!
You see before you
the rightful successor
to the legendary
throne of Gretagard:
The one and only
Garuda Dark-Black.
Can't say I saw
that curveball comin'!
Someone's disappeared
from the world of Naraku!
Messed-up stuff!
Crazy!
Who was it though?
Can't be good, going from
Naraku to that weird place!
Things are simply topsy-turvy!
Who am I kidding,
I don't get it either.