[LEAFA]
I, Divine Emperor Sigrdrifa,
heir to the Holy
Asgarthor Empire,
Beseech thee, oh moon,
source of all Asmegin,
to please bless the
people of our country
with a bountiful harvest
in the coming new year.
Bless our empire with
prosperity and long life.
[LEAFA]
And with that,
the New Year's prayer
has been concluded.
I can't help but wonder
who will conduct
the New Year's Ceremony back
home since I'm not there.
[YUUTO]
"Cornered Wolf."
Well, I'm glad you're back,
Big Brother.
Did you have fun on your
little midnight stroll?
You sound angry.
Did I do something wrong?
Yes and no.
It's just that being
your bodyguard
used to be my
prime responsibility,
but lately, it seems like
Chris is fulfilling that role.
Yeah, but that's only because
her skills are a bit more useful
for walking around undetected.
I'm well aware of her skills.
So, uh...
...in other news, we may need
to prepare a guest room.
[gasps]
How'd Mitsuki get here?
--Were you summoned?
--[LEAFA] Huh?
That's actually not Mitsuki.
This is Lady Leafa.
She's a princess
of the Jarl Clan.
You know, from over in the
Holy Asgarthor Empire?
I apologize for any rudeness
caused by my ignorance.
As it turns out, she was
traveling around in secret,
but upon finding her,
we believed it best to
welcome her as a guest.
So, here we are.
It's more rundown
than I expected.
[ALL gasping]
Our humble quarters are nothing
compared to an imperial palace.
I assure you that you'll have
the finest welcome we can offer.
Would it be all right
if I look around?
Of course, feel free to explore
as much as you like.
Since you're
staying here for now,
I should probably
go back to the inn
and inform your guards
of your whereabouts.
Yes. I'm sure they're
worried since I snuck out.
I'd appreciate it.
As usual, you did
an excellent job.
There's no need to
keep hiding, though.
It seems I wasn't
hiding well enough.
Detecting the unknown
is my specialty.
But, fortunately for you,
I don't believe it's Father's.
Thank goodness! If he
knew I was guarding him,
then he'd probably
be more on edge
when walking around the market.
Did you need something?
Lady Leafa, what do
you think of her?
She's quite powerful.
Yes, even if I were
to catch her off guard,
I don't think I could beat her.
That may be true, but her
skills are unrefined.
I would describe her
as a diamond in the rough.
I'm sure you're right.
Detecting fighting skill
is your specialty.
Well, she's no mere princess.
That said,
I don't believe she's
a threat to Father.
He's the Dark One?
Hard to believe.
[knocking on door]
[FELICIA]
Big Brother! It's Leafa!
[YUUTO] Did she manage
to find more trouble?
Yes, at the workshop!
[LEAFA]
Do you have wax in your ears?
Lord Yuuto said I could explore
the palace as much as I like,
so I do have permission!
I'm so sorry, My Lady,
but unfortunately
I have to see a pass!
I don't need a pass!
[YUUTO]
Oh, no!
Forgive me, Lady Leafa.
I'm afraid this
room is off limits.
Say what?
It's nothing personal, but entry
is forbidden to other clans.
[LEAFA]
Even me, Lord Yuuto?
Uh, well, the thing is...
Uh... Uh-huh.
In that case, I guess
I'll have to use force.
[INGRID] What the heck
is going on out here?
[INGRID]
Mitsuki? But how?
Did you get called
to this world too?
Actually, it's not
what you think, Ingrid.
She just looks like Mitsuki.
Okay, then who is she?
Oh, wow! I can't believe
I'm meeting the Lady Ingrid,
the famous blacksmith!
I've heard so many good things!
Uh... who are you again?
Princess of the Jarl Clan,
Lady Leafa.
The Jarl Clan?
Hey, they're old
customers of ours!
That's the third time now
somebody's mistaken me
for this Mitsuki person.
Where is this mysterious
girl everyone knows?
Well, pretty far away
at the moment, actually.
Ah, and could someone explain
what Lady Ingrid meant
about her being
"called to this world"?
That's a very unusual thing to
say to someone, don't you think?
Yeah, you've got a point there.
Listen, I know this might
be tough to believe,
but the truth is that I actually
came here to Yggdrasil
from another world entirely.
Oh? How exactly?
Uh... Well, um,
it'll sound crazy,
but in my world,
I looked into a holy mirror,
which I think was made
of elven copper,
and then, the next thing I know,
I was sent to this world
where Felicia was
standing in the room
performing the hidden
magic called Gleipnir.
If that is truly what happened,
then that means
that there should be an elven
copper mirror here in Iarnvithr.
But how could you know that?
Well, as it happens, the Empire
is the world's frontrunner
in the study of elven copper
and divine secret magics!
Please tell me more! It could
be extremely important.
I suppose.
And I do owe you for
saving me last night.
But first...
I am starving!
Can we have lunch?
Whoa! This is so delicious!
It's a hamburger, a dish we like
to make back in my world.
There are a few differences
since some of the ingredients
are hard to get here.
Whew! That was quite the feast.
Your weird food was oddly tasty!
Thank you. So, uh...
Right, of course.
What is it you would like
to know about secret magics?
Mostly, I'm just interested
in finding a way to get
back to my own world.
[LEAFA]
You can't go back?
No.
There's something odd about
the way you say it happened.
Oh, what's that?
[LEAFA] I don't feel that much
divine power emanating from you.
I'm not trying to sound mean,
but it's obvious
that you're a
below-average magic user.
Yes, I'm well aware of my
weakness in that regard.
Even with one half
of a pair of mirrors,
you don't possess
nearly enough power
to summon a person from a
different world by yourself.
I'm pretty strong, and not
even I could manage that.
Are you a magic user, too,
Lady Leafa?
Naturally, but I'm not
just any old magic user.
In fact, I happen to be
the most powerful one
--in all of Yggdrasil.
--[YUUTO groans]
Are you implying you
don't believe me?
No, I'm not saying that,
but I did do a bunch of research
on the top magic
users of this land,
and I don't remember seeing
your name anywhere on the list.
Go. Raising.
[YUUTO grunting]
What did you just do?
I can't move!
How dare you?
Explain yourself!
What? I was just demonstrating
my power to Lord Yuuto.
[FELICIA] Two runes?
You mean like Steinthor? How?
No! That's not possible!
There's only supposed
to be one other person
with two runes
in all of Yggdrasil.
But that would mean you're...
Oops, here we go.
You're actually the
Divine Emperor Sigrdrifa?
[sighs]
That was stupid of me.
I managed to blow my
cover on the first day.
[FELICIA]
Was I right?
Yes.
Before you is the
13th Divine Emperor
of the Holy Asgarthor Empire.
I am Lady Sigrdrifa!
[FELICIA]
Please forgive my impertinence!
[YUUTO]
Yeah, sorry.
So, can you please
undo the spell?
My face hurts.
[chuckles]
[LEAFA] Well, you see, there are
two major types of magic:
Spells with internal effects,
and spells with
external effects.
The spell I just used,
"Raising," is the internal kind.
[YUUTO]
Yeah, that's fascinating.
But the spell, please undo it.
My body is so heavy.
Because Raising is a spell
of the internal variety,
it will require an external
spell to negate it.
Some people are better at
certain spells than others.
[YUUTO]
Don't tell me.
I'm very good at
the internal spells
but terrible at external ones!
[YUUTO]
That's a really peppy way
of admitting you can't
undo the spell.
At least it was an abbreviated
one with no chanting or ritual.
That means it should expire
on its own after a week.
[YUUTO]
Felicia, can't you do something?
Sorry, Big Brother,
but it's too powerful
for me to undo.
If you're really desperate
to get it fixed sooner,
I'm sure Sigyn,
the Witch of Mithgarthor,
would be able to
undo it immediately.
[YUUTO]
Sigyn? From the Panther Clan?
Oh, good. So you
already know her!
There's a rumor that
she can use Fimbulvetr,
a spell that can supposedly
release one from their bonds.
Big Brother!
[YUUTO]
Then that light was...
[MITSUKI] Huh? You met a
girl who looks like me?
[YUUTO]
Yeah.
Her hair and eyes
are a different color,
but other than that, she could
practically be your twin.
What's her name?
[YUUTO on phone]
Leafa.
[gasps]
[YUUTO on phone]
Huh? What's wrong?
Nothing, her name just sounds
familiar for some reason.
[YUUTO]
Anyway, thanks to her,
I may have a lead
on getting home.
[MITSUKI screams]
Ow, my ear!
It's only a lead. There's still
a lot to figure out, okay?
Tell me everything!
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
So, if I have someone cast a
spell called Fimbulvetr on me,
then I should be
able to come home,
but the only one who can
do it works for an enemy clan.
[MITSUKI]
Don't give up hope just yet!
Maybe there's someone besides
Sigyn who can cast it.
Good idea! I'll start
looking into it right away.
Talking to you always
gets me fired up!
I believe I'll see
you again, Yuuto.
[YUUTO]
Here's to the New Year. A toast!
[CROWD]
A toast!
[CROWD laughing and cheering]
[groaning]
Man, these official
ceremonies are exhausting.
[FELICIA]
Big Brother,
this is a gift from all
of us for the New Year.
I love it!
That's so thoughtful
of all of you.
Right, time for the
unofficial ceremony.
We should probably keep
Lady Leafa's identity
a secret for now.
Sure! We can use
our private ceremony
to welcome
"Lady Leafa" properly!
Just leave everything
to me, Big Brother!
[sighs] I don't think
I can drink a drop more!
Here! You're almost empty!
Eat your fill
while you can, Effy!
A warrior never passes up
the opportunity to eat!
[ALBERTINA laughs]
That's some welcome!
I think it's wonderful,
Lord Yuuto!
I've never been to
a New Year banquet
that was quite
like this before.
-[YUUTO] Uh...
-Big Brother, listen...
...can I please have just
a little bit of your seed?
[CHRISTINA] Oh, you're
so funny, Auntie Linnea!
But the Claw Clan would
also like your seed.
[groaning]
It's so hot in here.
Don't rip your clothes off!
Oh, I beg your forgiveness,
Big Brother.
Would you prefer that I remove
them a bit more slowly?
[YUUTO]
Uh... What?
Okay, then, allow me to go next.
[YUUTO]
Huh?
Then I'm doing it, too.
[YUUTO]
No, don't!
I won't let you all beat me!
[YUUTO]
Hold on!
We'll join you.
--Yay!
--[YUUTO] Seriously?
Please, stop.
Stop stripping!
[LINNEA] I just want your seed!
Why is that so difficult?
[FELICIA]
No, me, first!
[CHRISTINA]
The Claw Clan has first claim!
[YUUTO] I told you I'm in love
with a girl back home!
So good!
--[GIRLS laughing]
--[YUUTO screaming]
-[YUUTO groaning]
-[ALL GIRLS] Huh?
[CHRISTINA] Father, Albertina
and I have just returned
from our most recent
scouting mission.
We have bad news.
We came across a Lightning
Clan army 8,000 strong,
and being led by none other
than Steinthor himself.
You did? And they're
heading here?
Yes. I apologize for not
spotting the force sooner.
Gather our troops immediately!
Right!
Oh, my! That's quite a view!
[YUUTO]
Twelve thousand men in all.
I'm sorry, but it looks like
I'll have to leave for a while.
I understand that you need
to protect your people,
but... can you really win?
I never fight a battle
if I know I can't win.
Although our Horn Clan
allies are still stuck
in a skirmish with
the Panther Clan,
which means we can't count
on them for reinforcements.
I feel a little bad that I've
spent three whole months here
and have done nothing to
reward you for your kindness.
Here, lean forward.
[YUUTO grunts]
Lady Leafa!
[BOTH gasping]
What'd you kiss me for?
[LEAFA]
That was a good luck kiss
from the Divine Emperor!
Try sounding less surprised
and a bit more grateful.
I am grateful.
I'd just rather you didn't.
That's the rudest thing
anyone's ever said to me!
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay. I can't expect
you to know all our customs.
All right then, I'll be waiting
to hear of your victory!
I have to say,
I didn't expect Fort Gashina
to fall to so quickly.
[CHRISTINA] The Lightning Clan
army made camp
in front of the fort.
They're waiting for
us here and here.
With our iron weapons,
we can typically hold our own
in straight-forward battles.
But if Steinthor
is leading them,
we'll be wasting our men's lives
without some kind of plan.
Right, time for another
plan from Han Xin.
We'll lure out the tiger.
Run, you lead the right flank.
Scarfior, the left.
In the center...
I can count on you to
watch my back, right?
Yes, of course. Just focus
on the vanguard, Father.
Okay, everyone,
onward to victory!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[FELICIA]
The Lightning Clan troops
sort of resemble an arrow.
Yeah, arrowhead formation.
It's an assault pattern,
and it looks like
Steinthor is leading it.
Wait. Is he riding a horse?
[FELICIA]
And he has a new weapon!
[YUUTO] I can't imagine
that being useful
for anything, though.
[STEIN] So those are
the wagon forts, huh?
[chuckles]
[SOLDIER A]
Crossbows, fire!
[yells]
Huh?
[FELICIA]
The crossbows aren't working!
Is that umbrella
seriously made of iron?
How on Earth does he manage
to wave it around like that?
Time for some payback!
Here you go!
--[STEIN shouts]
--[SOLDIERS shouting]
[YUUTO] You know, it's unfair
how much that guy cheats.
He broke through the wagon forts
with nothing but brute strength!
It'll be okay!
The plan was always
that they'd be broken
through eventually.
But isn't the Lightning Clan's
advance a little too strong?
What? Iron?
Yes, it would appear that
the Lightning Clan forces
are all equipped
with iron weapons.
Hold on. The Panther Clan!
You think there's a connection
between them, the weapons,
and Steinthor being
on horseback?
If they're working together,
then it explains everything.
This is bad.
Once again, I failed
to find out in time.
Our second rank
was broken through!
[YUUTO] Tell everyone to fall
back! Do not engage the enemy!
Messenger, go back
and inform Thjalfi
that we've broken through
the enemy's ranks!
Yuuto Suou must have
something up his sleeve.
Stay sharp, everyone!
Tell all units that it's time!
Deploy the kouyaku formation!
[horn sounding]
Let's go!
Onward!
What's going on?
[SOLDIER B]
Enemies from the north!
[SOLDIER C]
Ambushers from the south!
Calm down! We told you.
This is all just part of
the Wolf Clan's strategy!
[SOLDIER D] Sir, the enemy
is pushing back from the rear!
[THJALFI]
What?
Damn it!.
Kouyaku formation?
Yep. You deploy your
forces in two rows.
Then you make the enemy
think they're winning
and lure them in
where you crush them.
They fell for our trap
and jumped right into
the fangs of the Wolf.
[STEIN] Looks like you've
done it again, Yuuto Suou.
You really are
a clever leader.
[THJALFI]
Father!
I think we should withdraw.
Yes, I agree.
But not to our rear.
If we do that, then he'll
have us totally surrounded.
Death is behind us!
Tell our men
if they want to survive this,
then we need to run forward!
Don't worry. I'll open
the path for everyone!
[laughs]
[YUUTO] He saw the trap
and is still going forward?
Well, I don't know if it's
his idiocy or instinct at work,
but that was
the right answer.
Not that it will
do him much good.
We can take down as many
of your 8,000 men as we can,
Dolgthrasir!
Get out of my way!
[shouts]
It's about time you showed up!
[THJALFI]
Father!
[STEIN] Thjalfi, take our troops
and keep moving forward!
I'll handle things here!
Plus, if I don't take
the she-wolf's head,
I know that I'll regret it.
You heard him!
If you want to survive, you need
to push forward immediately!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
There's no turning back!
Big Brother,
it looks like they're going
to break the encirclement.
We have to motivate our forces
and defeat the enemy
no matter what!
Honestly, I didn't put
that many troops
to our front to begin with.
We won't follow them.
But why not? This could be
our chance at victory!
[YUUTO] I once read you should
never fight a desperate foe.
Right now,
Steinthor and his army
think their only chance
at survival is to go forward.
They're desperate.
For now, the first
battle is ours.
Let's move on.
[CHRISTINA]
Father! Father!
Terrible news!
I just saw mounted units
heading this way from the south,
and... they're 10,000 strong!
For real?
They're almost here.
I'm sorry.
But that's impossible.
I'm coming for what's mine,
Yuuto Suou.
There's nobody to bother us now.
Let's go!
[shouts, grunts]
Come on! What's the matter?
Can't you hit me?
The scrawny wolf is back!
Took you long enough!
Why don't you join your
men and run like a dog?
[shouts]
Well, at least things are
finally getting interesting.
Your skill is deflecting
my attacks, right?
[shouts]
Not anymore, though!
Nice try!
[grunts]
[yells]
Time to die!
Run, no!
You're too slow!
[grunts]
Scarfior!
You're next, she-wolf!
Hope you've got wings!
--What happened?
--Things are really bad!
We'll just have to use the power
of the preview to save them!
Say what now?
In his hour of need,
Linnea appears before him,
and the power of love has turned
her into the ultimate patriarch!
She trounces all
the enemies and...
I'm pretty sure it's not going
to go down that way.