[FELICIA singing]
La, la, la, la, la.
La, la, la.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la,.
[YUUTO]
"Phalanx.
A tightly-packed
formation of spearman
that was greatly effective back
in the time of Ancient Greece."
What are you doing
out here all alone, huh?
So late at night, no less.
[YUUTO] Oh, I was just
doing some research.
And how can you get onto
me for being out here
when you're the one
skinny-dipping in the dark?
[FELICIA giggling]
Wait a minute.
So are you complaining?
It's my job to make
your heart skip a beat.
I don't remember seeing
that on your resume.
Now don't forget we have
an important battle tomorrow.
Just promise me you won't
stay up too late, okay?
It'd be a shame if our patriarch
was too weary to give orders.
[YUUTO]
Don't worry.
I'll go get some sleep now.
It's funny, but I think the
stars are the only thing
that haven't changed for me.
[YUUTO]
"The Oath of the Chalice."
[SOLDIERS roaring]
[horses whinnying]
[screaming]
[SOLDIERS growling, grunting]
Wait a moment. No way.
Those are iron spears?
It can't be!
The battle has
turned in our favor.
Excellent work, Big Brother!
You're a splendid
commander as always.
[YUUTO]
The phalanx formation.
It's not like I came up
with it on my own.
I'd say Alexander the Great
and Nobunaga Oda
deserve the real credit.
Alexander the who?
I'm nothing but a dirty cheat.
Okay! Their forces are
on the verge of breaking!
It's time to finish this!
Raise the banners!
Let's get ready to charge!
[SOLDIERS roaring]
[YUUTO]
It's been two years
since I was summoned
here to Yggdrasil.
In this world, people will
gladly kill each other
over tiny pieces of land.
Those who are weak are often
oppressed and trampled upon.
Somehow in this world where I
didn't even speak the language,
I managed to rise to
a position of power
as the Patriarch
of the Wolf Clan.
A single order from
me can determine
whether somebody lives or dies.
[FELICIA gasps]
Watch out!
[YUUTO]
Thank you, Felicia!
Wow, it never ceases to amaze
just how strong you
Einherjar can be!
I think the arrow came
from that direction.
[YUUTO]
Horn Clan Einherjar!
[FELICIA]
Oh, my! That's a lot of arrows.
[YUUTO]
Seriously?
Leave them to me!
[FELICIA shouts]
Well, that wasn't
much of a challenge.
[YUUTO]
You're impressive as always.
I think you'd be an
awesome queen one day.
Well, seeing as you are
kind of like our king,
are you trying to suggest
that perhaps you'd like
to eventually marry me?
Uh...
I meant more like a Queen that
you'd see in a chess game maybe.
[FELICIA giggles]
You're always so silly!
Honestly, though, in my opinion,
that makes you
even more charming.
More importantly,
if the battle has
reached this far already,
the fighting on the front line
must be pretty intense.
[YUUTO] I hope Run's okay.
I'm worried.
I highly doubt you need
to worry about that one.
After all, she is the
strongest wolf, Mánagarmr.
She should be back any minute.
[FEMALE FLAG BEARER] SigRun of
the Wolf has just defeated
the Horn Clan's commander!
We're victorious!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
See, what did I tell you?
There was no reason
to be worried about her.
Yeah.
[RUN]
There you are, Father!
You okay?
You didn't get hurt or anything
during the battle, did you?
I'm not even sure how I
would manage to get hurt.
I'm nowhere near
the front lines.
I'm much more interested
to know how you are.
I'm fine, of course.
Thanks to the grace
of the Goddess,
I sustained no injuries.
Behold! I have zero scratches.
Good job. That's awesome news.
What do you want for a reward?
Just name your price,
and it'll be all yours.
Wait. Anything I want?
Sure, I mean, if it's
within my power to give.
You mean that? Okay.
[RUN]
Well, in that case,
I'd like to ask you
for a pat on the head.
That's really all you want?
A pat on the head from you
is the greatest reward
I could ever imagine!
Okay, I guess that's
easy enough to do.
[RÚN giggles]
You should see yourself, Run.
You're just like a
loyal little puppy!
[RÚN barking and panting]
[chuckles]
Excuse me? Is my request
somehow funny to you?
Nope, it's totally cool.
I wanted to ask you.
What'd you do with the Horn Clan
patriarch you captured?
Oh, I meant to tell you.
I've placed her in the custody
of our finest soldiers.
[YUUTO]
Right! Assemble the tents!
Prepare for peace negotiations!
This girl is the
Horn Clan patriarch?
Indeed. I believe that
her name is Linnea.
[YUUTO]
She's just a kid.
Hey, I may look young,
but I'm still a leader!
Please, we should at least
properly introduce ourselves.
My name is Yuuto.
I'm the patriarch
of the Wolf Clan.
I don't like to waste
time mincing words,
so I'll just come
out and ask you.
Will you become my new child?
[LINNEA]
Absolutely not!
You're delusional if you
think I'm going to serve
under a bunch of lowly dogs!
[FELICIA laughs] I'm sorry.
I don't mean to laugh,
but the only delusional
person here is you.
You dare mock me?
Once upon a time,
we were just dogs,
but that is no longer the case.
Thanks to our beloved patriarch,
we've been reborn into
something far greater.
Now, we are true wolves,
and we're more
powerful than ever!
You can't be serious!
That man-child is nothing
more than a frail boy!
Hold your tongue. You will
not insult our patriarch.
That's enough, both of you!
Remember, this girl is the
Patriarch of the Horn Clan.
You will treat her with respect.
I apologize for their conduct.
[LINNEA] No, I'm sorry
for calling you dogs.
[YUUTO]
"When someone is antagonized
through threats
and intimidation,
they become more accepting
of those who would offer
them a helping hand."
Negotiation Tactics 101.
So anyway, back to business.
Now, what were we talking about?
I had asked you to
become my child.
I already told you no!
Okay, then what about
becoming my little sister?
Your little sister?
That's the compromise
I'm willing to make.
Unlike a child,
a younger sister or brother
has different privileges,
and they aren't
bound by servitude.
Sorry. I can't.
I'm part of the Horn Clan.
[YUUTO]
Such a shame.
You've left me with no choice.
In that case, your city will
share the same fate as Van!
[gasps]
[CITIZENS screaming]
[LINNEA] You'd really slay
all those innocent people
and burn it to the ground?
If you refuse my patronage,
yes, I will!
[LINNEA whimpers]
Make your choice. Hurry up.
I'm not a very patient man.
[LINNEA sobs]
Fine, you win.
I'll become your sister.
But only your sister,
understand?
I won't be your child!
That works for me.
[YUUTO sighs]
[RUN] Father,
is something the matter?
You're not feeling ill, are you?
I'm good. Just really tired.
Thank goodness!
[FELICIA chuckles] You know,
lying on the floor like that
makes you seem a lot less scary
than the infamous leader
who goes around torching cities.
Of course, he's not scary.
He didn't burn anything.
He's not that type of man.
Father is far too kind to behave
in such a ruthless manner.
Well, it's not that
I'm kind, per se.
Naive? Definitely.
But having a story
that indicates differently
can sometimes limit
future bloodshed,
like it did today.
[FELICIA]
For what it's worth,
I've always found your naiveté
to be a very charming quality.
You should really try not
to be so hard on
yourself all the time.
Thank you for saying so,
Felicia.
It's only the truth.
You don't have to thank me,
especially since I'm the
one who summoned you.
It's the least I can do.
Hey, wait a sec!
I respect your charming
naive-uh-whatever it is, too!
[YUUTO]
Thank you as well, Run.
Oh, sure!
[YUUTO] Okay, it's time
to head back home.
Onward to Iarnvior!
[CITIZENS cheering]
[CROWD chanting] Sieg patriarch!
Sieg patriarch! Sieg patriarch!
It appears that you're still
as popular as ever, Big Brother.
Everything okay?
Huh? What? Yeah, sorry.
Why don't you try
answering your adoring crowd?
Right, I probably should, huh?
Ha!
[CITIZENS cheer]
Ah, home sweet home!
[BRUNO] It's good to see you've
returned safely, Lord Yuuto.
And congratulations. We heard
your victory was impressive.
All thanks to our soldiers.
You should know we prayed
to the goddess Angrbooa
so that the Wolf Clan
would triumph in battle.
Are they really trying
to say we won
because of their dumb prayers?
[FELICIA chuckles]
Anyway, I'm kinda in a rush.
So let's talk later!
[BRUNO]
Excuse me Lord Yuuto,
but don't you think
it's unacceptable
to speak to your uncles
in such a rude manner?
We are the younger brothers
of the last patriarch.
Show us some respect!
A relationship born of the
chalice must come first.
That has always been
the way of our people,
which I'm sure
you can understand.
Damn it! I'm in a hurry.
I'd be happy to
listen to your report
and relay it to him later.
[giggles]
Sounds good.Thank you!
[pants]
[YUUTO] I should've put it
in the sun more. There!
[phone ringing]
[MITSUKI]
There you are!
I've been so worried, Yuuto!
Thank goodness you're safe!
Sorry. I didn't mean
to worry you.
[YUUTO]
But I'm honestly doing great.
Good. I'm so glad.
It's wonderful to hear that.
[MITSUKI sniffs]
Oh, Yuuto. I've missed you.
[chuckles]
I've missed you too, Mitsuki.
So, uh, have you found
a way back home, yet?
[YUUTO on phone]
No, not yet.
[MITSUKI]
Oh.
Well, promise me you'll
keep trying, okay?
I'll be waiting for you
for as long as it takes.
[YUUTO]
I will.
[YUUTO] This place, Yggdrasil,
probably isn't another world.
I think it's on Earth.
Judging by the tools they
use and their culture,
it's a time period somewhere
between 1300 and 2000 BC.
Basically, its Earth during
the late Bronze Age.
It has to be, because the
constellations here
are the same as
the ones on Earth.
Based on their location,
I think it's somewhere in
the Northern Hemisphere,
but I'm not sure where exactly.
[FELICIA]
It's time to wake up.
The day awaits!
Uh, hey, good morning.
Good morning.
I hope you slept well.
It looks like it's going
to be a beautiful day.
I've brought you
a nice, fresh breakfast.
[sniffing]
Ah, it smells awesome!
Um, the rotor?
[YUUTO]
The rotary quern?
Yes, that's it.
Thanks to your great idea,
we can bake delicious
bread every single day!
Yeah, I'm always impressed
by how knowledgeable
you are, Father!
It's only because
of my smartphone.
Your smartphone?
Ah, it's been a while since
I've had a good night's rest.
I feel like I'm raring to go.
Yes, that much
seems fairly obvious.
Maybe I could help
you out with that.
It must be hard having
all that energy stored up.
Unfortunately,
I'm gonna have to pass,
but thank you for offering.
Oh?
I think your top half
and your bottom half
don't quite agree
with each other.
Stop it, Felicia,
or I will execute you for
making our lord uncomfortable!
[FELICIA] Listen, Run, it's
common knowledge that men have
to clean out their pipes
every once in a while,
or it can be bad
for their plumbing.
Wait. Is that how
it works? Really?
Be reasonable.
If it's not with us, it'll just
be with some other woman.
We might as well send him off
with some proper experience,
don't you think?
Well... that's a valid argument.
Wait, do you actually
believe her?
[RUN]
Okay then, I know that my body's
more muscular than curvy,
but I'll offer it to you anyway!
Uh, the only thing I want right
now is breakfast! I'm starving!
True. You shouldn't do
anything too strenuous
on an empty stomach.
He should really give
in to his urges.
If nothing else,
it might help relieve
some of the stress
from his daily duties.
If we're going to make an
oath with the Horn Clan,
they'll need weapons,
preferably of iron.
Do you think Ingrid
can make them?
[INGRID] All right everyone,
time to remove the slag!
No way, Yuuto?
[YUUTO] Hey! It's been
a while, huh, Ingrid?
Not sure why you look
so surprised, though.
Uh, no reason in particular.
I just didn't realize you were
already back in the city.
Some friend you are.
Everybody else seems
to know I'm here.
Hey, some of us have been
breaking our backs at the forge
since yesterday!
So I can't really spare
the time to think of you.
Well, I can always come
back later if you're busy.
You've already interrupted me!
There's no point
in you leaving now.
Might as well stick around.
Ahem.
Sorry, Lady Ingrid, but as
I've reminded you before,
you need to be more
respectful to the patriarch.
Apologize.
[INGRID yelps]
Are you serious? Okay then.
It's just kinda weird
since I've known him
for so long, you know?
And you know what they say?
Old habits die hard.
Anyway, I guess...
I'm trying to say
I'm sorry! Argh!
--[FELICIA and YUTTO laugh]
--Don't laugh, damn it!
Uh, I mean... please don't
laugh at me, sir.
You don't have
to change anything.
Honestly, I wouldn't
know what to think
if you were suddenly nice.
Yes, I agree.
When it's just the two
of you, I think it's fine
to use your regular names
and be more informal.
Wait. What do you mean?
Like alone?
I don't think she means
anything weird by it.
She just means, like,
if we were to make
something together again.
Right, of course, I knew that.
I mean, that makes
perfect sense, sir.
Oh, yeah. I wanted to tell you
the Horn Clan's patriarch
will be my new sister.
[INGRID]
The Horn Clan is joining us?
I think it'd be a good idea
for them to also
use iron weapons.
Sounds tricky, but okay then.
I mean, as you wish!
I know that it'll be
a lot of extra work.
I'm sure you can
handle it, though.
Thanks, Ingrid.
Yeah, right.
Leave it to me!
Uh, sir!
[giggles]
[ALEXIS]
Thank you for gathering here.
On this day, in the name
of the Divine Emperor,
I, Alexis,
will perform the ritual.
Join me in observing our
most sacred ceremony,
the Chalice of Allegiance.
[YUTTO] In Yggdrasil,
all the people in a clan
make an oath with the
patriarch over the chalice
and become his children
or younger siblings.
The ties created by the chalice
are stronger than
those of blood.
It's a holy ritual called
the Oath of Allegiance,
and it's meant to
bind a patriarch,
his children,
and siblings together.
That is how things are
done in this world.
This ritual should
make it possible
to rid the Wolf Clan
of all opposition
and bring peace to this realm.
All I want is to find
a way to get back home
without having to worry
about the people here.
[LINNEA]
Big Brother,
may I have a word with
you outside, please?
[YUUTO]
Sure. I don't mind at all.
[LINNEA] I'm sorry. I don't
mean to inconvenience you.
It's all right. What'd you
need to talk about?
[LINNEA] I wanted to ask that
you treat the Horn Clan people
with the same respect
you would your own.
Please, I beg of you!
Do what you want with me.
Just be kind to my people.
That's all I ask.
Uh, well, you know...
[YUUTO]
You're totally safe here.
[YUUTO] After all,
you're my new little sister,
so I would never hurt you.
Oh, Big Brother.
I... I don't know
how to thank you.
[footsteps]
[FELICIA]
Big Brother!
[YUUTO]
What's wrong, Felicia?
We've just received
a messenger pigeon
from Fort Horn at the border!
This is very serious,
so I'll get right to the point.
Four days ago,
one of the largest clans
to the west, the Hoof,
began an invasion of our
new sister nation, the Horn.
They've captured their
fort on the border.
Their forces number
around 10,000.
Wait, 10,000 soldiers?!
[ALL chattering]
The Horn Clan hasn't recovered
from their recent defeat,
and Linnea isn't there, either.
It's literally the perfect
time for an invasion.
It's my fault this happened.
Because I lost the battle.
[YUUTO]
I'm declaring this an emergency.
I propose we go to the rescue
of the Horn Clan immediately!
Whatever for, Lord Yuuto?
It's not as if the
Wolf Clan is under attack.
This sounds like the
Horn Clan's problem, not ours.
I agree with Bruno!
I feel bad for the Horn Clan,
but we only made the
pact earlier today!
We don't exactly
owe them anything.
What are you saying?
[BRUNO] The Horn Clan were our
rivals until a few hours ago.
We should have just
made them slaves!
But instead,
we made them siblings
out of the goodness
of our hearts.
It's just that you're still
rather young, Lord Yuuto.
You couldn't possibly understand
what you're asking.
Don't say another word.
I don't want to hear any more
of your rancid stupidity!
[ALL gasp]
[giggles]
[YUUTO]
What kind of people would we be
if we violated an oath
on the same day we made it?
The Wolf Clan should have
more pride than that.
[grunts]
[YUUTO]
We will aid the Horn Clan.
End of discussion!
My decision is final!
It's my sole mission in life
to help Big Brother relax!
Uh, wrong. It's my mission.
I'm sorry, Run.
I'm afraid you're not equipped
for this particular task.
What would I need exactly?
You'd need bigger
pillows obviously!
[RUN gasps]
Mine are so small!
Yes, but mine aren't!