[RUN]
Father.
[RUN] I was so rude
that night. Forgive me.
How did I end up
in this position?
Well, if nothing else,
I'll just go easy on her.
Prepare yourself!
[YUUTO shouts]
[RUN]
Just as I suspected.
We can't even use you
on the battlefield
as an infantry solider.
[grunts]
You won't make a fool out of me!
[shouts]
[RUN]
Too late!
No, this fight still isn't over!
Uh-oh.
[thudding]
Goddess of Angrboda.
Please watch over Father,
and bring victory
to the Wolf Clan.
[YUUTO] "The Lion that
Devours the Tiger."
[hawk screeches]
[YUUTO]
The time has come.
At last, the day has finally
come for me to crush those
wolf mongrels into dust.
I should warn you that
the Wolf Army is said
to use a variety of stratagems.
Wait here and see what
tactics they deploy.
Wait here?
Yes, I think that would
be the wisest action.
[STEIN scoffs]
But that's so boring!
Stop your whining
and do as Thjalif says.
Fine, I'll wait,
but only because you think
it's a good idea, Ving.
Okay, get ready!
Charge!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[SOLDIERS grunting]
We're losing too many
troops on the front lines.
What? It looks like the
shields aren't helping.
I recently heard a rumor
that the Wolf army prefers
to use iron weapons,
including the tips
of all their arrows.
What?
But iron is so valuable.
Why waste it on arrowheads?
[THJALFI]
I couldn't tell you, My Lord.
Hey, looks like it's working.
Our crossbow technology comes
from the distant future.
Its power and range is
superior to his bows.
And they seem to be
more accurate as well.
Yeah, that's true, but it
still has its disadvantages.
You know, their arrows
may fly pretty far
and do a lot of damage,
but something I've noticed is
that there's a great deal
of lag between volleys.
Don't falter! Keep going!
We need to break through
the enemy's lines faster!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
It looks like they're
getting closer.
Right. Recall the crossbows!
Phalanxes, advance!
[gong sounding]
[SOLDIERS shouting]
We're pushing on
their front lines,
but what the heck is
going on with our army?
Why does it look like they're
still losing this battle?
I believe what you're seeing is
the Wolf Army's main
infantry unit, the Phalanx.
They typically send in their
cavalry to support them.
So those weird bows of
theirs are a new weapon,
but everything else is their
same old bag of tricks?
Okay then, Thjalif.
I believe I've seen enough.
Ving, you take the left flank!
Thjalif, you take the right!
And as usual,
I'll take the middle.
[CHRISTINA] Our phalanxes
have the advantage.
This almost seems
a little too easy.
I think we had a harder time
fighting the Hoof Clan.
They're so uncoordinated.
Maybe it's their commander.
[YUUTO] Don't get me wrong. I do
think that guy's a total idiot.
But there's more to him.
No matter what, he's still
the leader of an army.
The Lightning Clan is known
for their strategists.
Oh, really? Well, part of
me wants nothing more
than to crush my opponent
when he's at his strongest.
But this isn't some game.
We can't give them a
chance to counterattack.
--[horn sounding]
--[reveille playing]
[RUN]
Right. That's the signal.
Everyone get ready!
We're going in!
Muspell squad, go! Attack!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[SCARFIOR]
A hammer and anvil strategy?
[YUUTO]
Yes, it's our specialty.
We use the phalanx
to pin down the enemy,
then hit them from
the side on horseback.
[CHRISTINA] But look, they just
sent out their chariots.
I'm the Managarmr
of the Wolf Clan.
My name is Siegrune!
And I am the Ivaldi of the
Lightning Clan, Thjalif!
So you're the strategist
I've heard so much about.
Finally, an opponent
worth fighting!
Come at me!
[yells]
[RUN, THJALIF yelling]
Now die!
Wow! You nearly
defeated Thjalif.
That's pretty impressive.
Wanna give me a try?
Let's see what you can do!
[RUN,STEIN grunting]
There aren't many things
that can withstand my attacks.
That's quite a sword.
[RUN, STEIN grunting]
[grunts]
Withdraw now!
Muspell squad, we're retreating!
[horn sounding]
[CHRISTINA]
Lord Yuuto,
the cavalry has just
left the battle.
So they repelled Run and
our anvil and hammer.
This is the first time
that our strategy
hasn't worked in a battle.
[FELICIA gasps]
Yes.
So, I told Run I wanted
her to get out of there
if she felt she
couldn't beat Steinthor.
I'm glad she did instead
of being stubborn.
The Tiger is a worthy foe,
which is no surprise
if even our ferocious
Managarmr had to retreat.
[YUUTO]
Well, this is a war.
No matter how strong
he may be alone,
we can still overwhelm
him with sheer numbers.
[STEIN grunting, shouting]
He's here.
[STEIN laughing]
[STEIN shouts]
The bravery of a fool for sure.
[FELICIA] "Bravery of a fool.
Bravery that doesn't think,
but just relies on its
own strength instead."
I believe you've
also described it as
"bravery that depends
entirely on physical force."
Is that right?
Wow, you remember
that whole speech?
Of course, it'd be
impossible for me
to forget any of your pearls
of wisdom, Big Brother!
--[distant explosion]
--[gasps]
Oh, looks like
we've got company.
[laughs]
[YUUTO] If brute strength
alone were enough to win,
there'd be no such
thing as tactics.
Just charging right into
our ranks with a chariot
makes him easy prey
for our phalanx.
Skewer that foolish
tiger on your spears!
[STIEN shouts]
[SOLDIERS grunting]
[STIEN]
Come on, everyone! Follow me!
What the hell is he doing?
Sir, our phalanx
is falling apart.
Seriously, that guy's a
worse cheater than I am.
Are you sure he's really human?
I had no idea the twin-runed
Einherjar was so powerful.
[YUUTO] His strength's enough
to uproot mountains,
and his chi could
cover the whole world.
Steinthor really does
remind me of Xiang Yu.
Lord Yuuto, I believe it
would be wise to retreat.
[YUUTO grunts] Guess we won't
be finishing things here.
Please allow me
to be the rearguard.
Try not to die.
Don't worry. I'd hate
to die in this place.
See you in Valhalla!
--[SOLDIERS shouting]
--[STEIN laughing]
[SCARFIOR]
Withdraw! We're retreating!
--[gong sounding]
--[STEIN] Huh?
[SCARFIOR] Don't panic!
Stay in formation!
Withdraw quickly!
You won't escape me!
What the--
[STEIN shouts]
You're a decent warrior.
I guess I'll get your name.
Fine. Scarfior.
Well, it looks like that
silver-haired she-wolf
isn't the best the Wolf Clan
had to offer after all.
So how is it that I haven't
heard of you before now?
If anything,
it's because I don't enjoy
being the center of attention.
Besides, of the two of us,
she's better to look at.
Don't worry. Give her
another two years,
and she'll surpass both my
strength and abilities.
I'm not interested
in the future.
I'm interested in
fighting you now!
While your words honor me,
I have no intention of fighting
you at this exact moment.
Come on. You're spoiling it!
I wanna have some fun!
[SCARFIOR]
Soldiers of the Lightning Clan!
What you see before you
on the ground is meteoric iron!
[SOLDIERS]
Huh?
[STEIN]
Hey, stop!
[SCARFIOR]
Iron! If you sell it,
then you'll never have to work
another day in your life!
[STEIN growls]
Let's go! After them!
Someone fetch me a horse!
Hey! I said after them!
Are you listening?
[THJALIF]
Hold on.
I think we should let Ving
handle their pursuit.
You should use this
opportunity to rest.
Come now. You can't
be serious, Thjalif!
I'm still capable of fighting!
But it's important to
take care of yourself.
How do you feel?
Do you need to eat?
[STEIN'S stomach grumbling]
[STEIN]
Uh...
I'll have the men prepare
a chariot worthy of you,
and we'll get you some
fresh clothes as well.
Is that your way of
telling me I should be
a little more presentable
in front of the troops?
Well, it's a fair point,
I guess.
Fine, we'll send Ving
to follow their army.
I'll rest up for
the next battle.
[STEIN] I guess Yuuto Suou
is a coward after all.
What did you say?
Ving's dead?
Yes, My Lord, I'm afraid he died
in a battle against Scarfior.
[STEIN screams]
Uncle Vingerhor is dead
because I suggested he
follow the Wolf Clan's army.
I can't apologize enough.
Why you!
You're right. It's your fault!
[STEIN shouts]
[coughs]
[gasps]
[STEIN]
I'm sorry! Are you okay?
I'm fine. This pain is nothing
compared to the sorrow
you must be feeling
over losing your blood brother.
[THJALIF groans]
Don't push yourself!
Please, don't worry
about me, My Lord.
You must focus on
winning this battle.
The soldiers in our
army are all on edge.
You'll have to lead them
to victory yourself.
Leave it to me.
I'll devour everything
the Wolf Clan has to offer!
[STEIN] Yuuto Suou.
I won't let him get away!
--[grunts]
--[horse whinnying]
Sorry, but I can't
let you go further.
Scarfior!
You killed my brother, Ving!
I will have vengeance!
[STEIN]
Now I get it.
Your ability is to parry
others' attacks, huh?
It looks like you
catch on quickly.
Hyah!
[STEIN]
Get back here, you coward!
My army's already
forded the river!
There's no point in me staying!
All right then,
troops, follow me!
Those stupid Wolf Clan weaklings
think they can escape us
just by crossing
some puny river?
Let's show them
just how powerful
the Lightning Clan can be!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
Okay, looks like their army
is gonna take the bait.
Why are you talking like
we're trying to catch fish?
Well, we are.
At least it's sort of
the same concept,
but instead of fishing,
we're setting a trap
that's big enough to
catch a foolish tiger.
Huh? I'm confused.
So, are tigers
supposed to be yummy?
No, not if you eat them while
they're still raw, Albertina.
You obviously have
to cook them first.
Well, look at you, continuing
to defy the laws of nature.
Impressive.
Aw, did your coward's legs
get tired of running away?
My legs feel fine.
However, My Lord has requested
that I stop you from
advancing further.
Now, I'm here.
And you believe you
can actually do it?
I don't have any illusions that
I could defeat a monstrous man
such as yourself
without a little help.
Hello again. I've come to
return the favor of humiliation.
I'm here because I
couldn't stand back
and let everyone else
have all the fun.
You really think
you can take me?
[FELICIA] We also invited
along the Brisingamen.
They're the Horn Clan's
four mighty Einherjar.
[SCARFIOR] That means you're
up against seven Einherjar.
Do you still think
you can defeat us?
[grunts]
Would you like to know what your
biggest weakness is, Steinthor?
I'll tell you. You think you're
so superior that you can't lose.
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[SCARFIOR] You left
your entire army behind.
Now, they'll all die!
Damn you!
Curse you all!
[gasps]
[ALL shouting]
[grunting]
Tell me something.
Has your tiny tiger
brain figured out
that this whole
fight was a trap?
You've lost!
You're weaklings, all of you!
You'll never defeat me!
[ALL gasp]
Huh?
You trap me?
That's the most hilarious
thing I've ever heard!
There's no way you can bring
a tiger like me down,
because no matter what,
I can still take all of you!
Even with all seven of us here,
we still can't beat him?
He might be beyond
our power to defeat.
Hey, give yourselves
a little more credit.
It's not like anybody
else has made a battle
this challenging
for me before.
You should all be proud.
[laughing]
Huh?
[SCARFIOR]
I told you at the start of this.
My orders were only to keep you
from advancing any further.
The seven of us
were a distraction.
This whole fight was just a
ruse to keep you in one spot.
You fought valiantly.
Of course, your fighting skills
don't really amount to much
when all you have is
the bravery of a fool.
Go!
Hey! What the--
Our lord is the ruler
of three great clans
who commands the laws of nature!
Maybe if you try hard, you might
be half the man he is one day!
What's that?
Can you hear it yet?
It's the howls of Jormungandr!
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS shouting]
Looks like you were
too busy fighting
to notice the rushing water!
Enjoy your complimentary bath!
I don't understand.
It should be impossible.
I can't lose.
[YUUTO]
Hey, you really came through.
Big Brother!
[YUUTO] Block the river so
all the water will build up.
Then break the dam down
at the right moment
as the enemy tries to cross.
I just can't believe
it worked out so well.
I've never heard of
such an amazing
battle strategy before.
You're a genius!
It's the Wei River Stratagem.
Steinthor reminded me of
general I once read about
named Xiang Yu.
Another general, Han Xin,
used this tactic to
defeat him in a battle.
Whoa! Big brother,
sometimes I think
you might actually be
the god of war's avatar!
[YUUTO]
Nah, I'm just a big cheater.
You get all the
credit for this one.
Huh? But why me though?
Well, having an
idea is one thing,
but executing it is another.
You brought the
townspeople together.
And it was you that was the one
who organized the
building of the dam.
Without your help, this idea
would have never panned out.
[LINNEA] I doubt even someone
as strong as Steinthor
could survive getting hit
by that rushing water.
This is goodbye to that idiot.
Not that I'm disagreeing
with the idiot part,
but you really didn't
like that man, huh?
No, I didn't.
I don't know if it's
talent he was born with,
or the power of the gods,
or Alfkipfer.
Whatever the heck it was,
he didn't earn it himself.
It wasn't the result
of effort or training.
And yet he was still so
arrogant about everything.
He was just cheating.
What do you mean, brother?
I don't get it. I'm sorry.
The reason he made me so angry
is because he reminds me of
myself and how I used to be.
[YUUTO]
What an absolute moron.
[grunting]
Oh, crap! That's pretty painful!
[sighs]
I actually lost.
And what makes matters worse
is it was to such a weak guy.
[laughs]
[STEIN]
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
I think I might have a
bunch of broken bones.
Well, I guess there's
no real point
in sweating the small stuff.
Hey.
[MITSUKI]
Oh, you're alive?
[YUUTO]
Hmph. Yeah, obviously.
[MITSUKI] You went a lot longer
than usual without calling,
so I started to worry you
might actually be dead.
[YUUTO]
Well, there was a lot to do,
and even more after
we won the battle.
Like what exactly?
[YUUTO] Uh, the Lightning
Clan's land is ours now,
so I had to figure out
who was going to rule it,
and I had to reward the
men who fought for us.
Then I had to compensate the
families of the fallen and--
Okay, okay, I get it!
[MITSUKI]
When are you coming home?
[YUUTO] Honestly, I don't know
how to get back right now.
Oh.
But once the Wolf Clan is
more powerful, I can do more.
Like, I'll be able to
research and stuff.
I know I'll find
a way back home.
Good. Don't keep
me waiting, okay?
Right. I promise.
You did a wonderful
job again this week!
Yeah, I don't feel like I got
that much screen time.
I'm starting to feel like
I'm getting less and less, too.
Okat, if I talk about
Big Brother some more,
maybe that'll help.
Oh, would it be okay
if I joined you?
Well, I kind of doubt
I could really stop you.
[FELICIA chuckles]