[GIRLS giggling]
[GIRL A]
Take this!
--[FELICIA] It's so cold!
--[GIRL A] Oh, you like it!
[GIRLS laughing]
Ah-ha!
[yelps]
[FELICIA]
Are you okay, Run?
[RUN]
I'm fine.
Wow. Quite a view, huh, Yuuto?
[YUUTO laughs]
Well, I certainly won't deny it.
[FELICIA]
Big Brother!
Look at this! Guess who
just caught something.
Listen, Yuuto, if you're
going to marry my sister,
I want you to know that
I strongly disapprove
of you having other
women on the side.
[YUUTO]
Hey, now.
I already told you there's
a girl I like waiting back home!
Yes, well, if you do something
to make Felicia cry...
...I'll murder you.
[YUUTO laughs, sighs]
[laughs]
[LOPTR]
"A Long-Awaited Revenge."
Thank you for your hard
work in the last battle.
Everyone did very well
against the Claw.
I'm proud of you all
and your various accomplishments
on the battlefield.
But I also have to
accept responsibility
for putting you in danger.
It was my failures as a leader
that put you in that place.
So I apologize to you all,
and I hope you
that can forgive me.
[BRUNO] Big Brother, please!
There's no reason to bow to us.
We were only able to defeat
such a powerful enemy
because you were leading
us as patriarch!
I don't need your flattery.
[BRUNO]
But I--
What the Wolf Clan needs
most in this moment
is a new Patriarch,
one who is not only powerful,
but knowledgeable,
and has youth on their side.
--[FARBAUTI] Yuuto.
--[LOPTR gasps]
As of today, you are the
Wolf Clan's Patriarch.
Uh... What?
[grunts]
What are you talking about?
I already told you that
I'm going back home
as soon as I can!
[FARBAUTI] I'm sorry, but I'm
unable to keep my promise.
You're the only one here
who has the ability
to keep the Wolf
Clan safe, Yuuto.
Wait! Loptr, he should do it!
He's way more capable at running
things than I would ever be!
Right, Loptr?
[LOPTR grunts]
Cut the act.
[YUUTO]
What act?
Your plan is to
make it look like
you don't want to
become patriarch,
and that you're only agreeing
to assume the role
is because
Father insists, right?
What a pitiful little strategy!
That's not it!
I swear I don't want to be
the patriarch, now or ever!
[LOPTR] Becoming the Wolf Clan's
patriarch was my dream.
I did everything in my power.
I wanted to protect
Felicia and our people,
to make us a more
powerful nation
that could stand up to
the Claw and Hoof Clans.
I was almost there.
I was so close.
But now you, of all people...
You want to take that from me?!
[gasps]
Brother, no!
[thudding]
--[CROWD gasps]
--[MAN A] The patriarch!
[gasps]
[FELICIA gasps]
Father.
But why?
[screams]
[SCARFIOR]
Don't let him escape!
He killed Father! After him!
[MAN B]
See if we can cut him off!
[SCARFIOR]
Someone help Father!
Hang in there!
Yuuto, please.
I'm here.
Promise me you'll take care
of the Wolf Clan's people.
You can't die.
Please listen.
If the day comes that you save
the Wolf Clan and go home,
then you'll have to
find somebody else
to be the new patriarch.
You should choose Loptr.
[YUUTO]
Pops, no! This is my fault.
Without my smartphone,
I'm just a normal teenage kid.
[YUUTO sobs]
I don't know anything
about how people feel
or how to manage this clan!
I'm nothing.
[screams]
[FELICIA]
Big Brother... Big Brother?
Big Brother?
[YUUTO]
Loptr?
Wait. What?
Uh, sorry.
[FELIIA]
It's fine.
--[door clatters]
--[ALBERTINA] Excuse us!
I hope we're not
interrupting you.
[YUUTO]
What's up?
Well, you see...
My big sister was throwing
the worst temper tantrum
and demanding
to come visit you.
I did no such thing!
All she does is go on and on
about the passionate night
that you two spent together,
like it's all she
can think about!
Shut up! No, I don't!
[YUUTO]
You shouldn't lie like that.
It's difficult to see her
in such a state of disarray.
Chris is lying!
Although, I guess it is true
that I wanted to see you today.
[CHRISTINA]
I knew it!
--[CHRISTINA laughs]
--[ALBERTINA whines]
So, tell me the real reason
you two have stopped by.
It looks like you've
figured us out.
Well done as always, Father.
[CHRISTINA]
There's news regarding a tribe
of the Hoof Clan, the Noatun.
They were conquered by a
nomadic Midgardian clan
called the Panther.
Wait. A Hoof tribe
was conquered?
And did you say the Panther?
Yes, they came with a mounted
army, thousands strong.
They what?
[CHRISTINA] And they
fired iron-tipped arrows
from horseback. They completely
annihilated the Hoof tribe.
[YUUTO] No! They shouldn't
have that kind of knowledge!
Iron weapons?
I didn't think there were
any clans besides ours
that even knew
how to make those.
That isn't what
worries me the most.
Given Yggdrasil's level of
technological advancement,
cavalry shouldn't be in use
for at least another
few centuries!
Unless someone managed
to get a hold
of our stirrup technology.
No, it can't be.
Brother.
Brother?
Probably the young
leader of the Wolf Clan
who's no longer here.
I've heard he possesses a rune
which allows him to copy
any kind of technology
he pleases.
[FELICIA] Yes, my brother
is definitely responsible.
Wait. What do you know, Felicia?
I realize now
I should have told you,
but about two weeks ago,
I received an unexpected
message from Loptr.
He asked me to turn my
back on the Wolf Clan,
to abandon you and join him.
And also, he said
he's the Patriarch
of the Panther Clan now.
You knew? For this long?
I'm so very sorry.
I'll accept any punishment
that you deem necessary.
But I would never desert you,
and I swear that you're
the only brother I'm loyal to!
Easy. It's okay. I'm just
glad that you told me.
Aw, Big Brother.
[YUUTO] Well, it sounds
like he's still harboring
a great deal of
resentment towards me.
[YUUTO] For now, let's send
our congratulations
to the new patriarch
of the Panther Clan
and pretend I know
nothing of his identity.
I should probably reply
to his message too,
to avoid any suspicion.
Yeah. I'm sure you know this,
but what you two just heard
stays between us four, Alchris.
We're separate people.
You shouldn't combine
our names like that.
Yes, we understand!
And I'll discipline my sister
if she so much as
breathes a word.
Excuse me?
Good plan.
[ALBERTINA]
What? No, it isn't!
[YUUTO]
Oh, man!
It's definitely not
gonna be an easy task
taking down the
Panther Clan's cavalry.
I better make that call
before my battery dies.
[phone ringing]
[MITSUKI]
Hello? Yuuto?
[YUUTO]
Hey! What's up?
So what did you do today?
[MITSUKI] Oh, you know,
just a normal day in paradise!
What about you?
Did something happen?
[YUUTO]
Huh?
Because it kinda sounds like
you're forcing yourself
to be cheerful.
[YUUTO] Once again,
you've managed to see
right through my act, Mitsuki.
Come on. I've known you
practically forever,
so there's nothing
you can get past me.
[YUUTO]
True.
Sometimes I think you
know me a little too well.
[MITSUKI]
Sounds rough.
Do you think everything
will be okay?
[YUUTO] Yeah, I'll come
up with something.
[MITSUKI]
That's not what I meant.
[MITSUKI] Do you really think
you'll be able to fight Loptr?
I'm the Patriarch of
the Wolf Clan now.
When the time does come,
I'll have no choice
but to fight him,
whether I want to or not.
[LOPTR] "The only brother
I'm loyal to is Yuuto." Heh.
I can't believe that
fool had the audacity
to forge a letter from
my beloved sister.
Well, it appears the time
has finally come, Yuuto,
for you to return what is
rightfully mine, all of it.
[SIGYN chuckles]
[FELICIA]
Big Brother!
[YUUTO] Looks like the
Panther Clan has attacked.
The town of Myrkvithr was taken.
This is bad news.
We might actually have to
fight the Panther Clan.
Summon our troops.
We're going to defend
the Horn Clan.
Right.
[YUUTO] We've still got
quite a ways to go
before we get to Myrkvithr.
[FELICIA]
Last we heard,
3,000 Panther Clan troops
had gathered there.
So are you absolutely sure
that Christina's
intelligence is correct?
Christina has never
been wrong before.
Though I have to admit
that the thought of facing
3,000 cavalrymen is
a sobering one. What's more--
--[SOLDIER A] Watch out!
--[SOLDIER B] It's the enemy!
Attack!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
Crap, they're here!
Units one through three,
move out!
I never expected them
to utilize the exact same
hit-and-run tactics we used
when we fought the Hoof Clan.
Man, it kinda sucks being
on the receiving end of things.
Do you think we should try
and wait until Run can get here?
They sure as hell aren't
going to wait for us.
Get down!
Covering the chariot with
sheet metal just saved us.
Still, though,
it's hard to believe
they were able to target
you from that far away.
Agreed, and I think it's only
fair to return the favor.
Fire!
[SCARFIOR] Unit Two, pass the
next crossbows to Unit One.
Give the unloaded
ones to Unit Three.
They're getting a lot better
at loading the crossbows.
Indeed.
Fire!
[grunts]
Retreat, men! Now!
Look, the enemy is withdrawing!
It was just an advance unit.
The real fight will begin when
we meet up with their main army.
[LOPTR]
For all your big talk,
you didn't manage to
accomplish much, Vali.
My information was bad!
They were firing their
crossbows one after the other!
I thought we'd be able
to shoot five times
in the period it took them
to release one volley!
Huh? Do you know
how they managed it?
[VALI] The men in the
first row would fire
while another row of
troops behind them
prepared the next round.
That's how they could
shoot so fast.
I see.
Very well. You may go.
Uh, Sir.
Narvi's report stated
that the Wolf Clan currently
has around 8,000 men.
It's amazing that
somebody so young
could have grown
his nation so much.
And he managed to do it
in less than a year.
Please, it's not as if he did
it all with his own power.
The boy himself
isn't anything special.
This time, he'll be the one
who falls into my trap.
[SOLDIERS shouting]
Charge!
We'll slam right
into their ranks!
Wait. They're back?
How many of them are there?
Big Brother,
we're completely surrounded!
Five thousand of them
at least, maybe more.
[SIGYN] They saw a few soldiers,
let their guard down,
and fell right into our trap.
[LOPTR] They might be able to
fire multiple crossbow shots,
but we can easily overwhelm
them with our numbers.
Even Yuuto's fancy phalanx
formation is completely useless
when they're surrounded
by an enemy.
That's what happens when
you put too much faith
in your smartphone.
I know exactly what
he's going to do,
and I can counter
anything he throws at us.
Hm?
[LOPTR scoffs] Does he think
he can offer me his cargo
in exchange for his life?
But then again, I suppose
I would expect nothing less
from a coward like Yuuto.
I will crush them down
to the last man!
All units, prepare to attack!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
He made it look like
he surrendered
and then ambushed us?
I swear there's no end
to his cowardice!
No matter.
[LOPTR]
Return fire!
[clanging]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
What is that?
[YUUTO] "By holding out
advantages to him,
he can cause the enemy to
approach of his own accord."
Brother, you've learned a
lot since I last saw you.
But you aren't the only
one who's been busy!
You're gonna see that I've
learned a thing or two myself.
Attack them!
Tear down those
strange carriages
and show them just what
the Panther Clan can do!
What in the hell
are those things?
See, I knew that since he was
familiar with my tactics,
he'd try to surround our army
with a huge cavalry force.
So I was waiting for my chance
to cause some massive
damage in a short time.
[YUUTO]
Fire!
[SOLDIERS groaning]
You know, when I
eventually die...
...I'm definitely
going to rot in hell.
[groaning continues]
[LOPTR grunts]
We should withdraw!
All that we're doing
at this point
is wasting the lives
of our cavalry men!
Withdraw now? We can't,
not when we're this close
to breaking through.
Please listen, Rungr.
We need to quit
while we're ahead.
Not yet.
I need you, Sigyn.
With your power,
we'd have the advantage.
With my power, but--
I get it!
Your intelligence is just
one of the reasons I love you!
Okay, then! Just leave
everything to me!
[SCARFIOR]
My Lord!
What's wrong?
[SCARFIOR] The enemy is
gathering their forces
in one spot.
Do you think they're planning
on retreating then?
No. Something seems strange.
--Like what?
--[SIGYN laughing]
--[gasps]
--[laughing continues]
What is that sound?
[laughing continues]
[SIGYN] The cursed hour,
when the sun fades away
and is replaced by darkness,
is now upon you.
The bonds of the holy pact,
made by God, begin to weaken.
And the chained, starving wolf
will be unleashed.
[YUUTO]
What's going on?
[SIGYN] Sharp fangs
of the howling wolf...
...shatter the mad idol
and bring forth the
chaos of catastrophe.
Fimbulvetr!
--Big Brother!
--What is it?
Look at yourself!
[YUUTO]
I'm glowing!
[SOLDIER C]
Enemy attack!
[SOLDIERS groaning]
What the hell is
wrong with them?
[yells]
[screams]
Your walls have fallen!
What's your plan now?
[LOPTR]
Thanks to Sigyn's hidden magics,
my soldiers have
turned into berserkers
who don't fear things
such as death!
Hold on!
[LOPTR]
Yuuto.
Well, well, we meet again.
Brother.
[LOPTR]
Don't call me that.
You and I stopped being
brothers a long time ago.
You took away everything
that ever mattered to me.
Now you'll pay!
[FELICIA]
Brother!
[LOPTR]
Felicia.
Why did you stop me?
[FELICIA] Because this
isn't the brother I know!
You killed Father,
and now, you're slaughtering
the people of the Wolf Clan
that you once vowed to protect!
Move aside! Do as your
brother tells you right now!
I'm not moving!
Just like I told you
in my letter,
the only brother
I'm loyal to is Yuuto!
[snarls]
I said move!
[gasps]
Brother!
Yuuto!
Listen, you're free
to hate me all you want!
But this? How could you?
You don't truly want to kill
your only sister, do you?
[LOPTR]
What the-- Whoa!
I am Siegrune,
Managarmr of the Wolf Clan!
I won't let you lay a
finger on Father!
It's Run!
Perfect timing!
Oh, yeah? I'll cut
you to pieces!
Whoa! Easy there, boy!
[SOLDIER D] The enemy's
horses are running away.
Yeah, why would they retreat?
What is happening?
Damn it!
Next time, Yuuto, I swear
I'll have your traitorous head!
Father!
Just let him go.
We need to let our army rest.
[RUN] I apologize it took
me so long to get here.
It must have been hard getting
used to riding the camel, huh?
Yes.
It's surprising, but horses
actually hate camels.
So I thought they'd be effective
against the cavalry.
[FELICIA]
Big Brother.
I'm sorry that you
had to protect me
from Loptr earlier today.
It's supposed to be
the other way around.
Hey, don't worry.
After all, you were up
against a terrible enemy.
You'll always be my second
in command, Felicia.
Thank you!
[YUUTO]
But...
...what was that light earlier?
Oh, Brother.
It's hard having siblings, huh?
Indeed.
Sometimes they steal your snacks
or tickle you
for no reason at all!
Uh, they do?
But when your little sister
is so cute, who cares?
--[FELICIA giggles]
--Hey, what is it?
Nothing! It's fine.
Sure, it is.