[ALBERTINA]
Look over there!
That's the
Wolf Patriarch, right?
[CHRISTINA]
Yes.
[CHRISTINA sneezes]
Hey, what's the matter, Chris?
You catch a cold?
I'm sure it's nothing, Al.
Come here for a second.
[ALBERTINA]
Huh?
[ALBERTINA yelps]
Why did you just
hug me all of a sudden?
[CHRISTINA laughs]
I can never tell what
you're thinking, you know?
Well, they say the quickest
way to recover from a cold
is to pass it off
to someone else.
Oh, yeah, I think I've
heard about that before.
[ALBERTINA gasps]
Wait. Do you want me to get it?
--[CHRISTINA coughing]
--[ALBERTINA crying]
[ALBERTINA] Stop it! I don't
wanna catch your gross cold!
You're so mean!
[CHRISTINA]
How can you say that?
Your darling little sister is
suffering from a terrible cold,
and you're not willing
to help her get better
as quickly as possible?
I never knew you were
such a cruel person, Al.
How awful.
Okay! I'll do my
best to help you!
How's this feel?
Perfect.
Yep, my big sister really
is the cutest person ever.
[YUUTO]
"Twin Runes and Twin Sisters."
Man, that ritual lasted forever.
You looked good up there.
Nice work, Big Brother!
And here.
Thanks, Linnea.
I'm really thirsty.
I... I want for us... for you...
I want you to marry me!
[YUUTO]
This is kind of awkward.
Oh! That dish is really tasty!
It's actually one
of my favorites.
It's a clan specialty.
I'm positive you'll
love it as well!
Yeah, okay.
So, what do you think of it?
Uh, well,
it's pretty interesting.
I think.
[LINNEA gasps]
I'm so glad!
It makes me happy knowing
that you enjoy
the Horn Clan's cuisine so much.
[YUUTO chuckles]
Oh, okay.
Huh?
Maybe... this one next.
Right. Open wide.
Uh, 'scuse me?
[RASMUS] Ah, I see you two
are getting along splendidly.
Like a couple of newlyweds.
[YUUTO gasps]
What did you say?
Hey! You shouldn't tease
us like that, Rasmus!
And it's especially
inappropriate
since the wedding was your idea!
Seriously?
[FELICIA]
Big Brother.
Don't forget about all the
eligible girls in the Wolf Clan.
[FELICIA]
What are you waiting for?
Put your arm around my shoulders
while they're still watching.
Oh, you!
What's wrong, Linnea?
You look upset.
Are you perhaps feeling a teensy
bit jealous at the moment?
No! Of course I'm not.
That would be childish.
Yes, it would be.
[FELICIA giggles]
Well, considering Brother's
rank and status,
if we were to marry, it'd be
my duty as his legal wife
to let him have
his concubines.
[CROWD gasps, murmurs]
[grunts]
[YUUTO] Who's that guy,
and what does he want?
[RUN gasps] It's Steinthor!
What the hell is he doing here?
Who's Steinthor?
He's currently serving
as the Patriarch of
the Lightning Clan.
They rule Vanaheimr.
[YUUTO] So he's the guy
I've heard about,
the king with the
heart of a tiger,
the dolgthrasir of Vanaheimr.
Alexis, why?
Why would you bring someone like
Steinthor to our celebration?
I think your tunic might be
a little tight, old man.
I am a ruler, after all.
I'm here to congratulate
my neighbor on their victory.
You murdered our last patriarch!
How dare you come here?
Really, I don't see why
you're making such a fuss
over a dead man.
[gasps]
[RASMUS]
Bastard!
What in the hell
is wrong with you?
Do you honestly think I'll
let you leave here alive
after you've insulted us?
I do.
Please calm down, Lord Rasmus.
I invited him here
as my honored guest.
So, I hope as a favor to me,
you can find it in your
heart to forgive him.
Well, seeing as you are a
priest of the Asgaror Empire
that rules over
all of Yggdrasil,
I guess I'll have no choice
but to retract my words.
Even if I don't agree with it.
That's in your
best interest, old man.
[ALL gasping]
You insolent little shit!
I will end you!
[RASMUS gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Why don't you calm down
before you give yourself
heart attack, old man? Heh.
[gasps]
What just happened?
[LINNEA]
That's Mjolnir...
a unique rune that transforms
all of its divine power
into a destructive energy.
So he's super-strong,
and he can somehow move
faster than lightning?
Yes, that's right.
Both his arms and legs
are exceptionally strong.
And you have his Megingjoro rune
to thank for that
particular ability.
[gasps]
That can't be.
You're saying he has
two different runes?
[LINNEA]
Yes.
He's a twin-runed Einherjar.
There's maybe only three at
most in all of Yggdrasil,
and he's one of them.
And I thought I was a cheater.
Well, let's see now.
Ah, there you are!
[RUN]
Stop right there!
Huh?
[RUN] I won't let you take
another step towards Father!
[STEIN]
That silver hair.
You must be the Wolves'
greatest champion.
It's Sieg-something
or other, right?
Playing dumb, huh?
Ah, well, I suppose the
details don't really matter.
I like your fighting spirit.
Though, you're no match for me.
[LINNEA] Looks like you've
made a real mess of things.
Huh, Lord Steinthor?
Then again, I guess a beast
couldn't possibly understand
the hearts of men.
I get it.
You're the new Patriarch of
the Horn Clan or whatever!
What's your name?
It starts with a letter.
Sorry, I've got nothing.
[LINNEA grunts]
You are so rude!
That's right!
It was Borghildr, wasn't it?
[LINNEA grunts]
Why you!
[ALL gasp]
[YUUTO]
I know you came here to see me.
Cut the crap and stop
harassing my people.
I see. You know how to
look intimidating, too.
[STEIN laughs]
It's been a while since
someone gave me a chill.
I think I might like you, yeah.
That doesn't make
me happy at all,
and I certainly don't like you.
Ouch, my feelings!
Got a question,
if that's okay with you.
What's your name,
Wolf Patriarch?
It's Yuuto.
Yuuto Suoh.
Yuuto Suoh, huh?
I'll try to make an effort
to remember that one.
[RUN, FELICIA sigh]
I won't lie, I was pretty
frightened for a moment.
That guy's strong, a total jerk,
but strong nonetheless.
[ALEXIS]
So, what did you think of him?
You certainly put yourself
in a lot of danger
to meet the Wolf Patriarch.
[STEIN scoffs]
[STEIN] For a man rumored
to destroy the entire world,
he was even more interesting
than I expected.
[ALEXIS] Hm... Then, will you
grant our request?
We're really depending
on your strength and abilities.
Please, Lord Steinthor.
[STEIN chuckles]
[STEIN]
Sure.
Finally, a fight that I can
actually get excited over.
[chuckles]
[MITSUKI on phone] Do you know
how worried I was about you?
How can you say that
you're going off to war,
and then not contact me
for three whole weeks?
[YUUTO]
I'm sorry, Mitsuki!
[MITSUKI] Look, I understand
that you're dealing with all
kinds of problems right now,
and that someone like me
could probably never get
what you're going through.
Yeah?
But you're managing
an entire clan now,
so I'm sure I don't
need to remind you
how important
the three C's are.
What are they?
Uh...
Let's see.
Contact, communication, and...
...consult?
That's right.
And newsflash, you haven't done
any of those things for me.
You could've at least texted me!
[YUUTO]
Right.
[MITSUKI sobs]
I'm sorry. I'm just...
so glad you're not dead.
[gasps]
[MITSUKI sobs]
[YUUTO]
Mitsuki, it's fine. I'm okay.
I should have called
you sooner. I'm sorry.
I never meant to make you worry.
Are things better?
Like, more peaceful, now?
Uh-huh.
[YUUTO]
They are.
[FELICIA] Everything seems to be
in order here in the market.
[YUUTO] Yes, but part of
my duty as the Patriarch
is to tour the city.
Gather around!
These books are imported
straight from the Claw Clan.
[FELICIA] You know, this
prosperity is only made possible
because of the paper
you invented.
And because our merchants are
selling it in other countries,
now the Wolf Clan's economy
is finally flourishing.
I can't take credit for
inventing paper, Felicia.
Uh...
[BOTH gasping]
This mother and child pair
are my top items for today!
Look at their snow-white skin,
unique to the people
of the north!
And I'm certain this
girl will grow up
to be as beautiful
as her dear mother.
I'm so scared.
Looks like he's a slave trader.
[YUUTO gasps]
Selling a girl that young?
[SLAVE TRADER]
So, do I have any takers?
Right here.
Oh, well, if it isn't
our Patriarch!
I'm so very honored
to serve you, sir!
How will you be paying?
Felicia.
Okay.
[FELICIA]
I believe this should suffice.
Thank you. That amount
is more than enough.
[GIRL whimpers]
It's okay. You're safe now.
Hey, guard, come over here!
Take these two to my
grand chamberlain.
See that they're
well taken care of.
Yes, sir!
Not that it matters.
It's still slavery.
[YUUTO] All I can do is change
what I can and help who I can.
One step at a time.
That's right.
[ALBERTINA]
Huh...
Interesting.
Aw, man.
How can there be this
much paperwork?
What did you expect?
We never dealt with it
after fighting the Horn Clan.
We immediately ran off
to a new battle.
So, now,
there's double the work.
That's true. Sorry.
This is probably the last
thing you wanna be doing.
It's fine.
If I help you with your work,
then it means I get
you all to myself.
[giggles]
[gasps]
Sure. In fact, I'm kind
of counting on that one.
Because you're,
you know, my, uh...
You're, you know...
You're my most trusted friend.
--[knocking]
--[door clatters]
[RUN]
Father? Pardon the interruption.
There are envoys
from the Claw here.
They're requesting an
audience with you now.
--In the audience chamber?
--[RUN] Yes.
A servant is escorting
them there now.
[YUUTO]
Twin sisters?
Uh, I'm sorry, but children
aren't allowed in here.
[RUN]
Lady Albertina, Lady Christina,
I thought I had asked you
to go with the servant
to the audience chamber.
Yes, I know.
But I just wanted to see
the face of my future husband.
[CHRISTINA]
I apologize.
I did tell her it
was a bad idea,
but I'm afraid she insisted.
I what? How can you say that
when it was your idea
to sneak in here after her?
Hey, don't you dare try and
pass the blame onto me, sis.
You were the one who said,
"I wanna see him.
I wanna see him,"
and pitched a fit like a baby.
You liar!
I mean, it's the truth,
but it's still mean.
Besides, you were the one
who brought it up
in the first place!
Classic Albertina slip-up.
You just admitted that
it was what happened.
--I win.
--What?
Chris, that trick was dirty!
No fair! No fair! No fair!
That's enough whining.
Now, apologize.
You're embarrassing us in
front of the Wolf Patriarch.
Don't you care what happens
to the Claw Clan's people?
[ALBERTINA gasps]
Uh, please forgive me.
I apologize.
My sister is so hopeless.
Please disregard
her childish nature.
Say what?
Wait. Why does it sound like
everything's my fault somehow?
[giggles]
That's what I mean by hopeless.
It's almost adorable.
[YUUTO]
Uh...
[groans]
[CHRISTINA]
Let's start over.
I am the Claw patriarch's
daughter by blood.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Christina.
And I'm her older sister,
Albertina!
[CHRISTINA] We were sent here by
order of the Claw Patriarch.
He wishes for my sister
and me to marry you
and become your wives.
I'm sure we'll all have
a very happy life together.
Huh?
[gasps]
Marry me?!
[YUUTO] Well, I never agreed
to marry either of you.
You can't just show up
and say things like that.
I'll have to ask you to leave.
Aw! No fair! You can't
just throw us out
after we've traveled
all the way here!
I have to agree.
The entire journey,
she kept telling me,
"I've heard that
he's really amazing,
but I've also heard he can
come off as kinda scary."
Then there's,
"Oh, I bet he's so handsome!"
And roleplaying.
[imitating YUUTO] "Albertina,
say that you'll be mine!
I want to be with you forever!"
[imitating ALBERTINA]
"Of course, Lord Yuuto!"
Considering how much she
just embarrassed herself,
the least you could do
is be a little bit nicer.
Show some compassion
for the poor girl.
[ALBERTINA whines]
Uh, now that you know
my deepest, darkest secrets,
please reconsider our offer!
Hey, even if Lord Yuuto
thinks you're hopeless,
I just want you to know:
I, your little sister, love you
and will never abandon you.
That didn't even make sense.
[ALBERTINA]
Wow, really? Thank you, Chris!
I'm sorry I'm so hopeless!
You're the only person
I can depend on!
You're so cute when you cry.
Is it me, or do they seem
a little high-maintenance?
I could be wrong,
but I suspect their Patriarch
may have sent them here
just to get some
peace and quiet.
Yeah, I agree.
[CHRISTINA]
Are you trying to suggest
that our Patriarch
wants to get rid of us?
[ALBERTINA]
How rude!
[YUUTO]
You heard that?
We sure did!
And don't act so surprised.
We are Einherjar, you know!
If they are indeed Einherjar,
it would be extremely rude
of us to ask them to leave.
Look, no matter
what you two may be,
it doesn't change the fact that
I never agreed to marry you.
Is it because you're too busy
preparing to marry the Patriarch
of the Horn Clan? Maybe?
[BOTH gasping]
Well, it looks like you
really do hear everything.
[CHRISTINA chuckles]
Uh-huh.
Including the truth about
the so-called massacre at Van,
you know, the city you always
mention in your negotiations?
[gasps]
[CHRISTINA] Of course, we
haven't told anybody about it.
I see your information-gathering
abilities are quite impressive.
I think you'd be better
suited to be my children.
[CHRISTINA]
Well, what a coincidence.
I wasn't really
all that interested
in this silly talk of marriage
or concubines anyway.
Honestly, I'd never let
you touch my sister.
Well, then what was the
point of coming here?
Do you want the truth?
The real reason we
came all this way was
to test you, Lord Yuuto.
That's it! I've heard enough!
I've held my tongue because
you're both princesses,
but you've been
nothing but rude!
I can't believe you would
dare test my father!
[YUUTO]
Hold on, Run.
The reason you told me the truth
is because you're satisfied
with what you see, right?
I am.
[CHRISTINA] Patriarch of
the Wolf Clan, Lord Yuuto,
we two sisters have never had
a father by oath before now.
We have but only
one life to give,
but we would gladly
give it to you,
the greatest
chalice of Yggdrasil.
[YUUTO]
I'm happy I impressed you,
but there's no need
for compliments now.
They're not just empty words,
Lord Yuuto.
We're quite serious
about this offer.
We would be very honored
to join your family.
Please consider it.
[YUUTO] I get the
feeling that these twins
might still be hiding
something from me.
Even so, they are Einherjar,
and I still have
that jerk Steinthor
that I have to worry about.
[YUUTO]
Okay, I'll consider it.
But you have to
prove yourselves.
[gasps] Hold on.
Why do we have to do that?
[YUUTO]
Good luck.
The chalice of the Wolf
patriarch is special.
You'll have to earn it.
I hope that one day I have
big boobs just like Felicia's!
I hear they grow better
if they're fondled.
Wait. Is that true? Then, Chris,
will you maybe touch--
No way.
Only an imposter would
refuse to fondle my chest!
Actually, I just wanna see you
worry about your teensy boobies.
I guess it is the real Chris.