[sighs]
[LINNEA gasps]
[LINNEA]
Big Brother, please...
Big Brother, please.
Right.
[YUUTO]
"Tactics of the Wolf."
It's only a matter of time
before the Hoof Clan
swallows up the Horn Clan.
[HORN trumpets]
--Huh? Ha!
--[SOLDIERS shouting]
I never imagined those
fools would come to us.
[shouting continues]
What? What the hell is this?
They only sent cavalry?
[SOLDIERS shouting]
It can't be!
How can they fight on horseback
in such a ferocious manner?
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[YNGVI]
Everyone remain calm!
Our foe is strange,
but small in number!
If we keep our heads,
we'll win this fight!
Huh?
[RUN] Looks like we're done
here for now! Let's go!
[growls]
Are they mocking me?
[SOLDIER A]
The Hoof Army is in chaos.
[LINNEA]
Siegrune is amazing.
She managed to
outwit and overwhelm
the forces of Yngvi,
Patriarch of the Hoof Clan.
And he's a powerful Einherjar
and the ruler of Alfheimr.
Thank you. You may go.
Ma'am.
[door clatters]
[sighs]
Still, though,
the stirrup devices
that the Wolf Clan came up
with are pretty incredible.
Riding a horse by itself
can be a difficult task,
but with the stirrups, you have
a stable platform to fight from.
Don't say another word!
I don't want to hear any more
of your rancid stupidity!
[ALL gasp]
[YUUTO]
We will aid the Horn Clan!
End of discussion!
My decision is final!
Okay, listen,
here's our plan of action.
Run!
Sir!
You lead the Muspell
squad ahead of us.
Pattern B, The Mongol.
Leave everything to me.
[YUUTO]
Jorgen!
Form up our main troops.
I want everyone ready
to head out by dawn.
As you wish, sir.
And Ingrid?
[INGRID]
Uh, yes sir?
We'll need more
of those stirrups.
I want you to share them
with Linnea's cavalry.
Wait. Is that a good idea?
After all, she is from
a different country.
That's true. But she's
still my little sister.
[INGRID]
Okay. I'm on it.
[YUUTO]
Linnea.
Um, yes?
[YUUTO] Get back to the
Horn Clan as soon as possible
and gather your troops.
Right, I'll go now.
[knocking]
[LINNEA]
Yes? Come in.
Excuse me, ma'am,
but the Wolf Army will be
arriving here shortly.
Okay, thank you!
Where is he?
[YUUTO]
Linnea!
[YUTO]
Sorry for the wait.
[LINNEA gasps]
Huh? What's wrong?
Are you sick?
It's not exactly the
best timing for that.
Nuh-uh! Mm-mm...
I'm just nervous because
we're going into battle soon!
I'll be okay!
Really? You can't let your
nervousness get the best of you.
If anything, you need
to keep a level head
so you can command your troops.
[LINNEA]
Right, of course.
You'll be fine.
So, where's the enemy now?
Our last report said they're
a half a day out by foot.
A half day.
Whew! Man, we barely made it.
'Kay! Meal time, everyone!
And anybody who wants
a cup of wine may have it.
--[SOLDIERS cheer]
--[LINNEA] Wha--
Wait. You're giving them
all food and booze
right before an
important battle?
For your army to be well fed
while the enemy is famished.
To simply be waiting at ease.
It's the art of husbanding
one's strength.
See? Make sense?
Um, not really. Sorry.
[YUUTO]
It's not my idea.
It's actually a line
from Sun Tzu.
You can't fight at full strength
when you're tired and hungry.
So we eat, okay?
Oh, that's a clever strategy,
Big Brother.
[YUUTO] I've already
sent someone on ahead
to put our plan into action.
With their help,
victory should be easy.
Wow! You really are amazing!
[YUUTO]
Run, please be safe.
We haven't slept a
damn wink in three days.
Any time we try
to break or rest,
we get attacked by
their blasted cavalry.
--[clanging]
--Huh?
Where are they?
[SOLDIER B]
Folkvangr, my lord!
It's not their cavalry unit.
We believe it's their
main army this time!
[YNGVI grunts]
--Assemble the men! Do it now!
--[SOLDIER B] Right.
It's starting.
And the Hoof Clan
is moving slowly.
That's good.
[SOLDIERS shouting]
Don't panic, men!
Form back up!
We can't.
We're practically
dead on our feet.
Looks like their troops
are exhausted.
Right! Get ready to charge!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
A densely-packed
formation of spears?
[chuckles] I heard
that the Wolf kid
had some rather
strange fighting ideas.
Guess I know now
the rumors were true.
Fascinating.
This'll be a good fight.
Hold on.
It only looks strong
from the front.
Chariots, strike their
main unit's flanks!
Let's see how those dogs
handle our counter attacks.
I bet the Wolf brat
won't see that coming.
The Hoof Army can't
keep up with our forces.
That's great!
We might actually win this.
[SOLDIER C] They're attacking
our left flank!
[LINNEA] They're here!
Just like Big Brother predicted.
Listen, there's a
distinct possibility
that the enemy will notice
the Phalanx's weak point
and attack from the side.
Hold strong if they do.
[gasps]
Don't worry. I'll take
care of everything.
[chuckles]
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[gasps]
[YNGVI laughs]
He's huge. Just massive!
The patriarch of the
Hoof clan must be a monster!
Hold strong! We have
to stay put no matter what
if we want to win this fight!
[SOLDIER D screams]
I knew the troops would
be weak on this side!
[SOLDIERS scream]
No. How are we supposed
to beat that demon?
Please, save me.
Save me, Big Brother!
This doesn't look good.
The Horn Clan's left flank
is being attacked by chariots.
Yes, I suspected they'd
discover our weakness.
Even so, it appears
to have happened faster
than you initially anticipated.
I was hoping
it would take longer,
but despite the
chaos in the field,
they discovered it
almost immediately
and launched a counterattack.
I should have
expected it. However...
"By holding out
advantages to him,
he can cause the enemy to
approach of his own accord."
I'll be the champion
of this battle of wits.
Even if I am cheating.
It looks like you didn't
plan for everything!
I'll shred you stupid
mutts into pieces!
They have one advantage,
and that's their chariots.
They'll utilize them
at every opportunity.
But that's where we
have the upper hand.
Because they've fallen
right into my trap.
It's go time.
Run, rip them to pieces!
Come out! Face me,
you cowardly mongrel!
[SOLDIER E]
Look! Over there!
[YNGVI grunts]
Back for more, eh?
Okay, our target is the
Hoof Patriarch, Yngvi!
All units, charge!
Victory is ours!
I am Siegrune, Managarmr of
the powerful Wolf Clan!
I see that you are
also a strong warrior.
Who are you?
I am the Patriarch
of the Hoof Clan
and ruler of Alfheimr.
You may call me Yngvi!
Good.
Then when I bring you down,
the battle will be over.
Come, Yngvi.
Today you die!
Hyah!
[YNGVI]
Not likely!
[shouts]
Your weapon is made
from iron, too?
Yes. Your army isn't the only
one who knows how to use iron!
[shouts]
[grunts]
Perhaps you and I will
fight again in Valhalla.
[gasps]
[shouts]
[coughs]
What... the hell is that weapon?
[RUN]
I'm told it's called a katana.
[YNGVI] Hmm. The world's...
so surprising.
But at least I got
to die at the hands
of a true warrior like you.
Thank you.
You have my thanks as well.
It was a great honor to fight
such a worthy adversary.
Let's meet again in Valhalla.
Yngvi has been slain by
Siegrune of the Wolf Clan.
We are victorious!
--[trumpets sounding]
--[SOLDIERS cheering]
[LINNEA whimpers]
Looks like we've won the battle.
Yeah. We have Run
to thank for that.
[YUUTO] Why are you in
the bath with me again?
[FELICIA] Because,
we're your escorts, silly,
and it's our job to make sure
you're safe at all times.
[RUN]
Plus, this is enemy territory.
Even bathing is far
more dangerous here.
Well, I'm clean enough, so I
think I'm gonna get out now.
[footsteps]
[LINNEA]
Uh, hi there.
[YUUTO]
Linnea?
What are you doing here?
[LINNEA] Well, I...
I have something important
to discuss with you,
Big Brother.
Uh, but can't it
wait until later?
Is it something you have
to talk about right now?
[LINNEA]
It can't wait.
I... I want for us...
For you...
I want you to marry me!
[ALL gasp]
What now?
Come again?
Listen, not only is it rude
to interrupt his bath,
but it's also rude to
make a request like that
out of the blue.
Etiquette demands
that at the very least,
you should offer to wash
Big Brother's back first,
and then you can
propose marriage to him!
Is that a real rule?
[LINNEA]
I'll do it.
[YUUTO]
Seriously?
Just turn around, so we
can get started already.
[LINNEA]
Wow, I never realized how
broad a man's shoulders
are compared to a girl's.
And you're so hard, Big Brother.
I'm what?
[LINNEA] I'm sorry.
Am I being too rough?
[YUUTO] Nope, you're doing
it just right.
[RUN clears throat]
I'd like to switch places
now if you don't mind.
Not a chance. If anything,
it's my turn next.
No way! I called it.
So what?
Look Run, you're
his daughter, remember?
I'm his sister,
so that means I go first.
[RUN growls]
Uh, you know what?
I think my back is
plenty clean now!
[BOTH]
What?
So, tell me what's up with
this sudden marriage proposal.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but it feels like it kinda
came out of nowhere.
Why? Is it really
such a strange request?
If you and I were
to get married,
then I think it would
help strengthen
the bond between our clans,
and even you can't deny
that both of our people
would be better off
because of it.
Look, I totally see the point
you're trying to make,
but you're the Patriarch
of the Horn Clan.
Do you really plan to
just abandon your title?
No, I don't.
Actually, my hope was
that you would agree
to be my husband and rule
the Horn Clan by my side.
What now?
What sort of nonsense is this?
You know father is the
Patriarch of the Wolf Clan!
You want him to
abandon his people?
I never said that!
He'd be free to keep ruling
the Wolf Clan as well!
But why should Big Brother
stick to ruling only one clan
when he can do more?
Wait. I don't think
you fully understand
what you're implying, Linnea.
[LINNEA]
I understand it quite well.
And I'll have you know
I gave this a lot of thought
before bringing it up to you.
I'm just having trouble
following your logic.
Frankly, this deal sounds
too good to be true,
and the Wolf Clan would benefit
more than the Horn Clan.
That's not...
[YUUTO]
She's right, Linnea.
It sounds a little
bit like a scheme.
Now, be honest and tell us
what you really want here.
Okay, then, I'll tell
you the whole story.
Who becomes the Patriarch
is determined
by your capability,
not by lineage.
Our traditions have
always dictated
that it's the strong
who should lead.
Hereditary rule
only leads to decay,
so Patriarchs
are chosen by merit.
[LINNEA]
I'm...
...a hereditary Patriarch.
[ALL gasp]
You shouldn't be sharing
that information with anyone!
If word ever got out, you could
lose your position as Patriarch!
Why does it matter if I tell you
when I'm already
trying to give it away?
Well, I get what
you're saying, but...
[LINNEA] For my father,
I was the precious child
he'd spent a long
time waiting for.
But I think he loved me
so much it blinded him.
[YUUTO]
And so because of that,
he made you his heir
instead of following tradition.
[LINNEA] Of course,
there were many people upset
that my father had appointed
an heir for himself.
I'm not even special,
like an Einherjar.
But I still wanted
to be our Patriarch!
I wanted to protect the things
my father loved and cared for!
I thought I could do it,
but I failed.
That's why I think someone
who's wonderful and smart,
like you, should lead
the Horn Clan,
instead of a stupid
hereditary fake like me.
So, please, I know I may not
be the best option available,
but I promise I'll
serve you forever.
If nothing else,
say you'll consider my offer.
Well, I, uh...
Might I interject?
While your offer
is very generous,
I would like to
remind our Patriarch
that it's not a decision
we should be making
by ourselves.
[YUUTO]
Uh... Yes, Felicia is right.
I should probably consult
with our clan members.
Right. Yes, of course.
And I apologize for
pressuring you like this.
Please, take your time.
I'll wait for your answer.
[YUUTO] Mm. We'll get back
to you. Sound good? Heh.
[YUUTO] What Linnea said
is really weighing on me.
And for that matter,
so is this dumb outfit.
[FELICIA giggles]
[FELICIA] You only have to
wear it for the victory ritual.
It's just for a little bit.
[YUUTO]
You know, from up here,
you can really see how different
the parts of Yggdrasil are.
If you were to take Big Sister
Linnea as your wife,
then the Horn Clan territory
would become part
of your domain.
[YUUTO] I'm not going
to marry her, Felicia.
[FELICIA]
But this is the perfect chance
to attack the Hoof Clan.
You could use this
land as a base,
and you'd be that much closer
to becoming the
ruler of Alfheimr.
Look, you make a good point,
but I still can't agree to it.
No matter how good of a deal
it may be for the Wolf Clan.
Right, please forgive me.
I became overzealous when
I heard we might be able
to take the entire Horn
Clan for ourselves.
But that's not
what you want, is it?
Felicia, why did you recommend
that I marry Linnea?
Because I know that
you want to go home.
[FELICIA] Come on. It's what you
think about the most, right?
So, I was worried that you were
going to disappear on us,
and it frightened me.
[YUUTO]
I see.
But if you become Patriarch
of the Horn Clan,
then you'll keep fighting
the other clans.
And if you do that,
I thought maybe
you'd stay here with us.
[crying]
But that's a selfish thing
for me to hope for.
Don't cry. I'm sorry.
There's no reason for you
to apologize, Big Brother.
But I am sorry.
No matter how tough things were,
you've always been
there to support me.
I'm the one who's been selfish.
That's why I'm sorry.
Big Brother.
I just want you to know
that it makes me very happy
you've been able to rely
on me these past two years.
No matter how selfish
you think it is,
I always want you to be
honest with your feelings!
I'd like that.
Is it possible you can forget
about what I said earlier?
And in return, I promise to
keep doing my best for you!
Sure.
In fact, I'm kind of
counting on that one.
Because you're,
you know, my, uh...
You're, you know...
You're my most trusted friend.
[FELICIA] Yes. I swear
I won't let you down!
I'll stop this wedding
between you and Linnea!
Don't worry about a thing.
Just leave this one to me, okay?
[YUUTO]
Thank you. I'd appreciate it.
Right!
Just don't do
anything too crazy.
Right!
I'm serious!
[BOTH laughing]
[STEIN] The Wolf Clan Patriarch
has defeated the Claw Clan,
the Horn Clan, and now,
the Hoof Clan as well.
I can't wait to meet him
and see what he's like.
[chuckling]
[LINNEA]
La, la, la. La, la, la.
You look pretty happy.
Of course, I'm gonna be
Big Brother's wife,
so I'm learning to sing in case
I ever need to cheer him up.
Wait. That's not true!
Watch. Soon, I'll make my debut
as the first singing,
dancing Patriarch!
This preview was useless.