There's nobody to bother
us now. Let's go!
[BOTH yells]
What's the matter?
Can't you hit me?
The scrawny wolf is back!
Took you long enough!
Why don't you join your
men and run like a dog?
[shouts]
Well, at least things are
finally getting interesting.
Your skill is deflecting
my attacks, right?
[yells]
Not anymore, though!
Nice try!
[yells]
--[gasps]
--[grunts]
[shouts]
Time to die!
Run, no!
You're too slow!
[grunts]
Scarfior!
You're next, she-wolf!
Hope you've got wings!
[growls]
[STEINTHOR]
"Proof of a Great Ruler."
Steinthor! How dare you!
[STEIN] What's wrong?
Did I hit a nerve, she-wolf?
[chuckles]
If you won't move...
...I'll make you!
[gasps]
[laughs]
[shouts]
Come on now! It's like
you're not even trying!
[yells]
[BOTH grunt]
[STEIN] Aw! It looks like you've
got some fight in you after all.
[THJALFI] Father! The Panther
Clan is preparing
to attack the Wolf
Clan's main army, sir!
They are?!
Really? Well, that was fast.
I guess I can't
let my guard down
around my masked brother
for even a moment.
We should join him
as soon as we can.
--I won't let you!
--Huh?
Come on. You can't be
serious right now.
Haven't I embarrassed
you enough?
Unless you want to end up
like your fallen friend,
then you had better
get out of my way.
[growls]
You bastard!
[yells]
[SOLDIER A]
Are we going to be okay?
[SOLDIER 2]
What's going on?
This is bad. Ten thousand
cavalrymen can only mean...
That we're going up
against the Panther Clan.
They've got us between a
rock and a hard place.
[FELICIA] Big Brother,
it might be best if we retreat.
[FELICIA] There are some
battles that cannot be won.
You are a brilliant leader,
but even you can't be
victorious every single time.
We should just withdraw for the
time being and try to regroup.
I agree.
With both the Lightning Clan
and the Panther Clan
pursuing us,
then a retreat would be best.
That can't be the only option.
I know it's a difficult choice
to make, but even so...
[YUUTO]
If we run away now,
then the enemy
will swarm after us.
They'll chase us back
into our own territory,
and our lands will suffer
greatly as a result.
Our men will be killed,
and our women and children
will be sold as slaves.
[YUUTO]
The Wolf Clan is my family.
Everyone in it looks up to me
as a brother or a father.
[YUUTO] Sometimes you need
to be cruel, be calculating.
[YUUTO]
At least, that's what the cheats
I've relied on this
entire time have told me.
But... I won't!
I won't just abandon my family
like some kind of lowly coward!
Of course, you won't.
For this battle, I'm using
a cheap little technique
you're so famous for, Yuuto.
I suspected from the beginning
that you'd set a trap like this.
It appears that I'm
several steps ahead
of whatever game you're playing.
Attention, Soldiers of
the Panther Clan!
It's time to avenge
our past humiliation!
This is our moment!
Prepare to engage!
All units, attack now!
[SOLDIERS yells]
What now, Father? How do
you want us to proceed?
I'm not sure.
Do you want me to
call Run back to us?
Unfortunately, I don't think
calling Run back
is going to help.
There has to be another plan
I haven't thought of yet.
How frustrating!
If only I had the kind
of power Steinthor did,
things would be different!
Big Brother?
Did you think of something
new that will help us?
Yeah. Well, new for me.
[SOLDIERS shouts]
It's no good!
We're outnumbered!
[SOLDIERS shouting, groaning]
[LOPTR chuckles]
That's right, men!
We'll slay them all!
Slaughter them like
the mutts they are!
[SOLDIER B groans]
It's over.
We can't win against
an army that big!
Maybe we should
give up. Retreat.
--[gong sounds]
--[BOTH] Huh?
[YUUTO]
To the front lines!
--[SOLDIER C] Huh?
--Did you all hear that?
[SOLDIER D]
Look, it's our banners!
--[SOLDIER E] Hey.
--[SOLDIER F] What's going on?
[grumbles]
[SOLDIER G] The patriarch!
It's the patriarch!
Hold your ground,
Champions of the Wolf Clan!
Take up your spears
and get into formation!
Rebuild the wagon forts,
quickly!
The fight's not over!
We will prevail!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
It's the patriarch!
Lord Yuuto will surely
lead us to victory!
Are you truly going to
the front lines, Big Brother?
I am. The Lightning Clan
always has the highest morale.
That's because Steinthor
is right there
at the front with them.
[CHRISTINA]
I think I get it.
You've never been
on the front before,
so if you go now, you'll be
able to inspire our soldiers.
You want to boost their morale
the way Steinthor does.
That's right, and I know
that it's a dangerous
move for me to make.
But because our
situation is so dire,
it's more important than
ever to unite our army.
[SOLDIERS cheers]
--[SOLDIER A] Patriarch!
--[SOLDIER B] He's really here!
[LOPTR]
Damn you, Yuuto.
Attention, men!
Behold the Patriarch
of the Wolf Clan!
There is Yuuto Suou!
He is your target!
I order you to go forth
and capture him!
I promise to reward any man
who brings him to me!
Yeah! Let's take down that cur!
That reward will be mine!
Die, you scum!
Please, men, believe.
Please put your faith in me!
[SOLDIER A]
Did you see Lord Yuuto just now?
[SOLDIER B]
The Patriarch is so brave!
Hail Lord Yuuto!
With Lord Yuuto as our leader,
the Wolf Clan is stronger
than ever before!
[SOLDIER C] He brought peace
and prosperity back to our land.
[SOLDIER D]
Because of him,
my family has bread
to eat every day.
[SOLDIER E]
He even sent my son to school.
I believe in him.
I have complete
faith in Lord Yuuto,
the savior of the Wolf Clan!
[SOLDIER F]
That's right! Me too!
What the--
The Wolf Clan's soldiers.
[ALL gasp]
[SOLDIERS yell]
Our Patriarch was right
about this battle!
Come on! We can
still be victorious!
We won't let you scoundrels
lay a hand on Lord Yuuto!
Protect the patriarch
at all costs!
Don't let 'em hurt the
Wolf Clan's savior!
[LOPTR grumbles]
This can't be!
How are our forces
being pushed back?
Way to go! This was a
splendid idea, Big Brother!
Considering that
I'm no Steinthor,
I'm honestly surprised that
it boosted their morale so much.
Don't say that!
From the soldiers here
on this battlefield
to the people back at home,
you are the Wolf Clan's savior!
Uh...
[STEIN]
Come on!
[RUN yells]
What's the matter?
Does the she-wolf need a break?
Not at all!
[BOTH grunting]
[STEIN] Hmph. Sure you
don't need to rest?
Damn you!
[SOLDIER A]
We're gonna be okay!
[SOLDIER B]
The Patriarch is here!
[SOLDIER C]
Lord Yuuto!
No way! Is it possible Father
is truly on the front lines?
[STEIN laughs]
Oh, my! You don't say?
Yuuto Suou never
ceases to amaze me.
Things are finally starting
to get interesting!
All these years, I had no idea
men like him even existed.
My father...
My father is...
[STEIN] Heh! It's been fun,
but I think I'll see
what your precious
patriarch is up to.
[RUN] Hey, I told you earlier
that I'm not letting you leave.
[STEIN scoffs]
Let's not be ridiculous.
It's not like you'll ever
be able to defeat me.
I have more important
matters to attend to.
Business with Yuuto Suou!
And this time, I'll win.
He may be the worthiest
adversary I've ever faced,
but still...
This time I have no intention
of losing to that man!
[RUN] Well, I have no intention
of losing to you, Steinthor!
Huh?
[RUN] It's a new technique,
and I'm still practicing it.
But now...
Huh?
[RUN]
It's my last chance.
[STEIN]
That's a new stance.
[RUN] Yes, it's a move
that Father taught me.
[STEIN] Oh? Sounds like it might
actually be interesting, then.
Let's go.
Heh! I'll give you a chance,
but I'm done going easy on you!
[STEIN yells]
[STEIN laughs]
Some technique!
How disappointing.
Right then, it's time
to say goodbye!
[groans]
[STEIN laughs]
Nice move, she-wolf.
[SOLDIER A] The Muspell Squad
has captured Fort Gashina!
We've won!
[SOLDIER B] Reinforcements!
The Muspell Squad is here!
So, we made it through?
[SOLDIERS cheers]
Big Brother!
Looks like the squad
finally made it!
The truth is I never
intended to engage you
in straight-forward
battle, Steinthor.
Not this time.
You see, my goal was always
to cut off the path
to your supply lines
as well as your escape route.
Though I do have to say,
I didn't think you'd
actually get this close
to defeating our troops.
Let's go! The counterattack
begins now!
[SOLDIERS cheers]
[laughs]
[STEIN] Every time I meet
him on the battlefield,
he comes up with some new
trick or plan to outsmart me.
I'm starting to think
that man might be a magician.
Well, as much as
I hate to admit this,
it'd probably be a good idea
for me to take my leave.
Hey, just so you know,
that attack really hurt.
Of course it did.
You can thank my father.
He's the one who taught
me how to do that.
[STEIN]
Tell me, what's your name?
The Managarmr of the Wolf Clan.
I'm Siegrune.
Siegrune's a pretty good name.
I'll remember that.
Okay, men, temporary retreat.
Go on ahead. I'll hold them off!
Father, no! We would
never leave without you!
Yeah, that's right! If anything,
we'll hold off the enemy
while you escape to safety!
No way. I'm not leaving a
single one of you behind, men.
Steinthor, get back here!
Please give your predecessor
my regards, Siegrune.
Huh?
[STEIN]
Okay, men, move out!
[gasps]
Scarfior!
Oh, no! No!
--[Scarfior breaths]
--[RUN gasps]
[RUN]
Scarfior?
I can't believe
you're still alive.
[RUN]
Let's tend to those wounds.
Come on, my friend.
Father is waiting for us.
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[LOPTR]
Impossible.
Even after we joined our forces
with the Lightning Clan,
we're still losing this war?
Not only did he steal
my position as patriarch,
but he's a better general, too?
Sigyn, I command you to
open up a pathway to Yuuto.
[YUUTO] This is good.
We managed to fend them off.
Right, Felicia?
He's coming. See?
Loptr!
They're not stopping him?
If I had to guess, it's probably
because of Sigyn
and her spellsong.
The Panther Clan's witch?
Do you really think so?
Yes.
Time to die, Yuuto!
The battle is over!
What are you doing?
Just retreat already!
Shut up!
All I have to do is kill
you here and claim my victory!
I won't let you!
You had better get out
of my way, Felicia!
--[FELICIA shouts]
--[YUUTO] No!
Seriously? You'd attack
your own sister?
Please, Big Brother,
you have to get to safety now.
Ha! There's always somebody
around to take the blow for you,
isn't that right, Yuuto?
You really are just
a useless coward!
You can't do anything your own.
You're worthless!
Please, you have to get away!
[YUUTO]
No! I'm not going to leave you
to face him on your own!
[LOPTR]
Yuuto! I won't let you escape.
It's time you and I
finished this once and for all!
[SIGYN sings]
[SIGYN] The effect of the
spellsong is coming to an end.
[LOPTR yells]
[BOTH grunting]
So, you've learned how to
dodge my attacks, huh?
You bet I have!
Because I haven't been
skipping my fighting lessons!
I'm not the worthless
kid I used to be.
I'm sick of always having
to be protected.
I wanted to be able
to stand up for myself!
You see, I don't want
to lose anyone else.
No one's dying
for me ever again!
Oh, Big Brother!
Time to die!
You first!
You're done!
[BOTH grunting]
Damn you, Yuuto.
Loptr.
Are you okay?
[SIGYN sings]
It's her!
Another spell?
Yes, one that even I could feel.
I'm sure that's
Sigyn's spellsong.
But why?
[SIGYN]
The bonds of the holy pact...
...made by God begin to weaken,
and the chained,
starving wolf will be unleashed.
Fimbulvetr!
[FELICIA] Big Brother,
your body's disappearing!
--[YUUTO] Felicia!
--What's happening?
Take this!
Why?
[gasps] No! Please,
don't leave us, Big Brother!
I beg you!
Listen, I don't
want this either!
What are we going to do?
I'm sorry.
[sobs]
Don't leave me. Big Brother!
--[SOLDIER A] Father!
--[SOLDIER B] This way!
[FELICIA]
What should we do?
[MITSUKI]
Huh?
Uh?
[footsteps]
gasps
Yuuto?
Uh, Mitsuki?
Felicia, where's Father at?
Uh, Run, I don't know
how to tell you this...
Wait. Has he already
gone to sleep?
That's not exactly
where he went.
Well, he must be exhausted
after that last battle.
I'll just go see
if he needs anything!
Poor Run! I don't know how
to tell her what happened.