[YUUTO]
Man, another failure.
You know, I'm starting to think
that making a cup out of glass
is just something you made up.
[YUUTO]
It's more like I suck at it.
Do you wanna give
it a try, Ingrid?
[gasps]
[YUUTO] Oh, I guess you
wouldn't want my germs, huh?
I'll get you a pipe
I haven't used yet.
No, that one's okay, really!
It doesn't bother me at all.
What I mean is...
...I'll just use yours.
[YUUTO]
I'll keep it steady for you.
Just relax and
blow in it slowly.
Uh, okay.
[INGRID] I can't relax with
him behind me like that!
[INGRID chuckles]
Awesome work!
You know, I bet we could
mass-produce these things.
Really? You think so?
[YUUTO] You have a
knack for making stuff.
[YUUTO]
I want you to stay by my side.
Don't ever leave me.
Stay by your side?
[YUUTO]
Is something wrong?
[INGRID gasps]
No, everything's perfectly fine!
[YUUTO]
Hm?
[INGRID] Anyway, why are you
still touching me? Get off!
[FELICIA]
"Valkyrie's Day Off."
Why did you call me here?
Am I in trouble or something?
Not at all.
It's just that I heard
Lord Yuuto has taken quite
a liking to you, young lady.
Because of that,
we thought he might like
to have you around more.
Yes, please don't worry.
If Big Brother likes you,
then it means
we can all be friends
and do lots of
fun things together.
That's right.
Wow. Thank you.
I'm so honored!
Now, the reason I've
called you all here
is because I want to
discuss something important.
It's a matter that
concerns Lord Yuuto.
As you know, Father possesses
a great deal of knowledge,
and his talent for military
tactics is unmatched.
Yet he shows no arrogance
and consistently puts in
more effort than anyone.
I'm sure that everybody
here can agree
that his perseverance,
hard work, and incredible skill
are the driving forces behind
the Wolf Clan's
current prosperity.
I propose we band together
and find a way for
Father to relax,
so he has the opportunity
to rest his body and soul.
That makes sense,
and I certainly agree
that Father has more than
earned a little time off,
but I'm not even sure
how we would go
about doing that.
[JORGEN] I was thinking
we could have him take
a short vacation in the
foothills of Mt. Surtsey.
[JORGEN] He's been so busy
governing the country,
it seems rather unfair
that he hasn't had any
time to relax in it.
Not to mention, this would
be a great opportunity
to get closer to him.
[ALL giggling]
[MITSUKI]
Whoa!
[YUUTO]
Huh? What's wrong, Mitsuki?
[gasp] Uh, sorry. I almost
fell out of my chair.
I just had this weird
chill run down my spine.
What a strange feeling!
Think you're getting
sick or something?
Maybe you've caught a cold.
[MITSUKI]
Hm... No.
It wasn't really
that kind of chill.
[FELICIA] And that's why we all
think it would be a good idea
for you to go on a trip
out to the country
and take a little
time for yourself.
Where'd this come from?
It seems a little strange
for me to take a vacation
while everyone else
is working so hard.
Listen, Father, if you do
nothing but work all of the time
then you're going
to make yourself sick.
Precisely.
And it's not like
we're telling you
to take a month off or anything.
Okay, I'll go. Just stop
looking at me like that.
That's great!
A group vacation, yay!
Uh, who said that
you were coming?
But, sis, I wanna relax too!
Just leave it to us.
We'll make all the
necessary preparations.
[FELICIA giggles]
[EPHERIA chuckles]
Huh?
[EPHERIA yelps]
Listen, Jorgen...
Yes?
I'm going to have to
leave you in charge
of Iarnvior for a few days.
Do you think you can handle it?
Yes, I can take care of
your responsibilities here,
but it's important
to the Wolf Clan
that you take some
time for yourself.
Why is it so important?
[JORGEN] As long as you
remain in good health
and continue to be
our Patriarch,
the Wolf Clan's prosperity
and fortune will be assured
for many decades to come.
If I didn't know better,
I'd think you were trying
to tell me not to
go back to Japan.
[JORGEN chuckles]
[YUUTO]
Still, there's no guarantee
that the Wolf Clan
will stay in power
after I go back home, is there?
[JORGEN] Honestly, you're
overthinking this vacation.
Trust me. It'll be easier to
give in to the girls' request.
[YUUTO] Yeah. I suppose
it would be nice
to have a few days to
relax and enjoy myself.
[YUUTO] Nice! I like the
look of this place.
[YUUTO sighing]
This is exactly
what I need right now.
[ALBERTINA laughing] Look out,
hot spring, here I come!
[CHRISTINA]
Al, wait!
You shouldn't run
when it's so slippery!
[ALBERTINA]
Ha!
Excuse me. This hot
spring is occupied!
What's the big deal?
You know we've been with
you this whole time, right?
Wait. Seriously?
[ALBERTINA giggles]
Look, can you go
somewhere else, please?
I really prefer to
bathe by myself.
[CHRISTINA]
I'm afraid that's not possible.
You need your bodyguards here.
I don't!
Nobody's gonna assassinate me
in the middle of nowhere!
[CHRISTINA] I never said
anything about assassins.
Honestly, I'm more worried
about you being eaten
by a bear or something.
Well, I kinda doubt
you'd be able to stop me
from becoming a bear's lunch.
So, you should go get
Run or somebody.
Okay, fair enough.
Jeez. I'll just have to
sneak out of here quickly
while she's off grabbing Run.
Nice try, but my backup
is actually already on the way.
Huh? They are?
Great.
What?
No way those bears
will get to you now!
I'm starting to think
there are no bears!
[CHRISTINA giggles] Oh, well,
better safe than sorry.
[YUUTO]
Why are you doing this to me?!
[FELICIA]
It's so peaceful.
It really is like a paradise.
[RUN]
Indeed.
This is the optimal environment
for Father to relax in.
Yes, there's nothing more
refreshing than a hot spring.
[RUN] Aren't you going
to take your towel off?
Like, in front of other people?
[LINNEA] This is my first time
ever going a hot spring.
I could definitely
get used to this.
[sighs]
[ALBERTINA laughs]
Look, Mister Monkey, I'm naked!
Whoa!
You'll have to excuse
my older sister.
She still has a lot to learn
when it comes to
acting like a lady.
Uh, since I'm a slave,
should I even be bathing
with everyone else?
Because this kinda
feels inappropriate.
Just take your
towel off already.
No!
I'm starting to think I'll
never have privacy again.
What'cha doing all alone?
Sulking in the corner?
You should come talk with us
instead of standing
over here by yourself.
[YUUTO]
No, thank you!
Don't worry. I actually caught
a quick glimpse of it earlier,
and it's rather impressive.
You know, I think
I'm starting to overheat!
--Bye now.
--[CHRISTINA gasps]
You can't get out already!
I haven't had a chance
to wash your back yet!
Linnea did it last time, so it's
only fair that I get a turn!
She's absolutely right,
Big Brother.
Huh?!
[CHRISTINA chuckles]
[YUUTO sighs]
[YUUTO]
Do what you want.
[YUUTO] Hold on a second.
What's going on here?
[FELICIA] After our previous
failure, we all got together
and discussed future
bathing sessions,
which included what would be
the most efficient method
to serve you.
And we drew lots to see
where everybody sits,
so it's extra-fair.
[sighs]
We're all set.
Whenever you're ready,
we can get started.
[YUUTO] What the heck?
I didn't expect this to happen.
But it's too late for me
to try and back out now.
"A prince should guard himself,
above all things,
against hatred and contempt.
It makes him contemptible
to be considered fickle,
frivolous, and irresolute."
That's what Machiavelli said.
So I have no choice
but to endure!
Whatever. I don't care.
Let's get this over with, okay?
But once you guys are done,
I'm definitely leaving.
Right. Then we'll
get started. Excuse me.
[GIRLS]
Here we go!
[EPHERIA groans]
[YUUTO yelps]
Felicia, what are you
using to scrub me?
Because it does not
feel like a washcloth.
[FELICIA]
I'm using my breasts, naturally.
[YUUTO]
Why? Just why?
I told you I was thinking
of the best way to serve you.
And what better way than
washing you with my own body?
Maybe use a scrub
brush or something.
[YUUTO yelps] Whoa, Run!
What did you just do?
I'm seeing to the cleanliness
of your toes by licking them.
[YUUTO]
You're doing what now?!
I didn't hurt you, did I?
No, but I guarantee you
that is not the issue here!
Well, Felicia told me that
I might damage your skin
if I used anything else.
So we thought the best
course of action would be
for me to use my tongue instead.
Are you kidding me, Felicia?
Don't tell her things like that!
[FELICIA giggles]
Those two are only
so close to Big Brother
because they're his advisers.
I won't let that intimidate me!
The same goes for me!
I'm determined to show
Yuuto how grateful I am, too!
Stubbornness is
your super power.
Use it for good, not evil!
[ALBERTINA] Okay!
I wanna clean Father, too!
[CHRISTINA]
Actually, it looks like
we've got everything covered
wash-wise, but if you want,
you can dry him off
with this linen cloth.
[EPHERIA]
I think I'm too young
to be witnessing
this sort of thing.
[ALBERTINA]
Scrubbity, scrub, scrub!
Look at me. I'm helping!
--[YUUTO gasps]
--[GIRLS giggle]
[YUUTO]
Can't... take... it.
--[FELICIA] Big Brother!
--[RUN] Father!
--[LINNEA] Big Brother!
--[INGRID] Yuuto!
--[ALBERTINA] Father!
--[EPHERIA] Master!
[GIRLS]
We're sorry. Please forgive us.
So, what was the
point of all that?
I've made it abundantly clear
that I prefer to bathe alone.
Yes, but...
It's just that we wanted
to try to repay you
for all the wonderful things
you've done for us
these past two years.
And if you're going to be
leaving us someday,
then we want to do
as much as we can now
in order to help you.
Fine, okay.
Then I'll let you all serve
me for the rest of the trip.
But you have to
wear your clothes!
And no getting too close either!
Got it?
[GIRLS]
We understand!
Okay, well now that we've got
your permission to proceed,
how about next we help you relax
with a nice group massage?
Huh?
[LINNEA]
Great idea!
Okay, I don't think you're
grasping the concept
of "not too close."
So let's just go to bed,
and we'll be nice and rested
for Al and Chris's
chalice ceremony tomorrow!
But won't you be able to
sleep that much better
if you're nice and
relaxed beforehand?
[ALBERTINA]
Massage! Massage!
[GIRLS laugh]
[YUUTP yells]
[YUUTO] Wait! Can't we
talk about this first?
Maybe we should do
something else!
We could all tell stories
or braid each other's hair!
Stop it! Stop it! That tickles!
[YUUTO groans]
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[ALBERTINA groaning]
Ow. My tummy hurts so much.
I really ate too much this time.
Well, maybe in the future,
you'll learn a
little self-control.
[ALBERTINA grunts] At least
I didn't eat everything.
[CHRISTINA]
Good job.
[YUUTO yawns]
We're finally finished!
I've never seen a chalice
ritual get so noisy before.
You performed
your part excellently.
[LINNEA]
Big Brother!
[YUUTO]
Linnea!
As your younger sister,
allow me to congratulate you
on adding another two members
to our growing family.
Well, when somebody's done
something impressive,
it's only proper to
reward them for it.
I think that's the key
in getting talented people
to join your cause.
Oh, by the way, did you hear?
I mean, about Steinthor.
Yeah, I heard.
I still can't believe that
idiot survived the river.
But there's no reason to worry,
because it's not like he
could ever beat you in battle.
I'm not anything special myself.
I'm simply lucky to be
surrounded by amazing people.
I owe everything to you guys.
Right?
[RUN gasps]
Huh?
Um, yeah, sure.
I guess.
[INGRID]
Here you go.
Personally, I think it's
even better than before.
[STEIN]
You'll never defeat me!
[gasps]
[sighs]
Hey, now, I'll have you know
that sword happens to be
one of my finest creations.
Do you have some kind of
problem with it or something?
No, it's great.
I'm very satisfied with it.
It's a beautiful piece.
Thank you, Ingrid.
[INGRID] Yeah, well,
you don't look very satisfied.
Uh, I am.
It's just that you made
this katana, right?
Yeah, why do you ask?
Are you lookin' for a fight?
Because I will give you one!
I didn't mean to insult you--
I don't care whether
you meant to or not.
Now you had better tell me what
the deal was with that sigh!
And you'd better give
me a good answer,
or I'll never make
you a weapon again!
Don't even joke about that!
[INGRID] Then I suggest
you start explaining!
What exactly did the sigh mean?
Fine, I'll tell you.
Here goes.
See, the thing is,
I was thinking about
how it wasn't Father
who made this
sword for me, so...
So?
What I'm trying to say is
that I wanted Father to make
the katana for me instead.
[RUN] When I think
about losing the weapon
that Father came up with,
I feel like I've also lost
the sense of safety and
joy that it brought me.
It's just gone.
To be perfectly honest,
I'm almost afraid
to fight without it
because it makes me
feel less sure of myself.
I see.
Hello there, Ingrid.
I wanted to ask if I could get
your help with something.
Hello, Father.
I'm glad you're here too, Run.
Perfect timing.
You'll never believe what I got
from a merchant who came
to the chalice ritual.
[gasps]
Careful! Otherwise,
you might cut yourself!
The hilt.
Yeah, I'm afraid the
hilt was a lost cause,
but the blade seems
to be intact.
I'm sure Ingrid can
fix it for you.
I'm just so glad to
finally have it back.
I don't think she heard me.
I don't think so, either.
[FELICIA laughs] She's happy,
and that's what matters.
[INGRID] Well, it looks like
I have more work to do.
By the way, Yuuto, how's the
whole glass thing going?
Pretty well, I think!
Let's go to the bazaar
and take a look.
It's always best to see
things with your own eyes.
Wow, the market's even
more crowded than usual.
Iarnvior is the only place
where you can buy
blown glass, after all.
So, I guess, in the end,
all that work was worth it.
Even though a certain someone
was making it hard
to concentrate.
[YUUTO]
Hm. I know it wasn't easy,
but we're making a fortune now.
And all thanks to
your wisdom, Big Brother.
Now the Wolf Clan will be even
more prosperous than before.
The poverty we experienced
two years ago
feels like ancient history.
[YUUTO]
That's good and all,
but we don't have the
resources we need
to do anything with that wealth.
There aren't enough talented
people to do the jobs
that will help the Wolf Clan
continue to grow.
Here, Master, I brought
you something to drink.
Great. Thank you!
[EPHERIA yelps]
[YUUTO groans]
[EPHERIA gasps]
Oops! I'm so sorry!
Oh, no! What have I done?
I don't know why I'm so clumsy!
Please forgive me, Master.
I'll do anything!
Relax. I'm not going to get
angry over a little water.
But I...
[ALL giggling]
I'm sure you're still getting
used to your new life here.
But thanks for
everything you do.
Uh, no. There's nothing
to thank me for.
I'm not as helpful
as the others.
You sure?
Uh-huh.
I may have lost my friends
and my big house,
but in the end,
you saved me and my mother,
so I want to do more
to repay your kindness.
I'm just not good
at anything yet.
Please don't worry about
repaying me, Epheria.
Now come on, we have
some yummy dessert here.
Oh, no! I could never!
There's no way
that I'm worthy enough
to eat the same dessert
as you, Master!
Well, that's a problem.
See, I'm actually not
a big fan of sweets,
but it would be rude to
the person who made it
to let it go uneaten.
It sure would help me out
if someone would
finish it for me.
I really shouldn't do that.
It isn't proper.
Go on. Eat it before it
goes stale. It's tasty.
[EPHERIA gasps] Okay.
Thank you. You're so kind.
Oh, wow!
It really is tasty!
What's this?
It's so delicious
it made you cry?
Yes, but the taste isn't
the only reason.
It just reminded me
of when I used to eat
these sorts of things
with my mom and dad,
back before I was a slave.
It sounds like you've
had a rough time, too.
Never mind.
I'm sorry if I made you
remember something unpleasant.
It's fine!
Thank you again for
the delicious dessert!
You're welcome.
Hold on a second.
Hey, Effy, come here.
Can you read that
sign across the way?
[EPHERIA]
At the wool merchant's stall?
It says, "One byg of silver
for 360 byg of wool."
Okay, that's plenty.
Now, you can have as
much of this as you like.
[EPHERIA gasps]
There's so much.
I couldn't possibly
take all this!
Of course you can.
Besides, I owe you for
the idea you just gave me.
[FELICIA]
Compulsory education?
Yeah, that's right.
Did you see how Effy could
read the sign at the market?
I did.
It she seems as though she
and her mom were quite well off
prior to becoming slaves.
Agreed. It gave me an idea.
You see, with a
proper education,
even small children like
Effy can learn to read.
Sorry, Yuuto.
I'm not following.
To put it bluntly,
the clan's literacy rate
is disastrously low.
And if we don't
address that problem,
we'll always have a
limited talent pool.
--Right.
--Okay?
What I'm saying is, I think
we should see to it
that every child from
the ages of 7 to 15
is given at least
a basic education.
But tuition would be expensive
and difficult for many
parents to afford.
And I feel like it
would be a little cruel
to force them to pay for
it against their will.
You don't have to
worry about that.
We'll make it so they can
attend school for free.
What?
The Wolf Clan can cover
all the expenses,
the teachers, the supplies,
the buildings.
Whatever it is they need
in order to be successful.
[GIRLS gasp]
We're making a ton of money
from our glassware.
It won't be long
before it exceeds
what we've ever made
from selling paper.
"No principality is secure
without having its own forces.
On the contrary, it's dependent
on good fortune,
not having the valor
which would defend it.
It has always been the
judgment of wise men
that nothing can
be so uncertain
as fame or power not founded
on its own strength."
Got it?
The only thing I got from that
is that you're about
to do something crazy.
It may seem like very
little to start with.
But if we start the process now,
in five or ten years' time,
it will reap a great benefit
for the Wolf Clan
and its people.
I see now.
If we don't have enough
talented people,
then we just have to start
developing our own.
That's exactly right.
[FELICIA] It sounds like
Brother's trying to plan
for what will happen
after he leaves us.
[INGRID]
It's a good idea.
Especially when you consider
how bad you used to be at
reading compared to Epheria.
Yeah. Hopefully,
the children of the Wolf Clan
catch on faster than I did.
[INGRID]
I bet they will.
[YUUTO]
Be nice.
I've learned a lot in the two
years since I've come here.
[LOPTR]
Glad to have you aboard, Yuuto.
The hot spring was so fun!
I think hectic and noisy
is more like it.
You'd be less grouchy
if you'd actually
done some swimming.
Swimming isn't the point
of going to a hot spring,
you dummy!
Then what do you do in them?
Soak in the water and relax.
Okay, we should go back
and try it right now!
We can't go all
the time, you know!