I am gonna get a ton of experience points for this guy!
Behind you!
Ugh!
Uh!
He slaughtered the big guy
and got the other two off his back.
And... he did it in a split second!
You played a vital role in getting rid of
covert operatives back then, did you not?
It truly has been a while, hasn't it, Bulat?
It's you, General Liver!
Former General, actually.
Ever since Master Esdeath saved my
life. I have been her devoted servant.
Huh?
Is this the same guy Bro was talking
about in the story from his past?
If things were different, I'd be
drinking a toast to our reunion.
But since they're not, I'm going to have to kill you.
The mission comes first!
I couldn't have said it better myself.
General Esdeath's wishes will be realized.
And to ensure that I am successful,
she gave me this Imperial Arm!
The Black Marlin, it's a ring-type weapon.
It was crafted from the organs of aquatic
Danger Beasts with the power to control water.
As such, whoever wears it can
manipulate any liquid at will.
If this is our battlefield, Lady
Luck is certainly smiling upon me.
So you fight with water now.
Rather convenient that your boss is an ice user.
General Esdeath can create ice out of thin air.
Do not elevate me to her level.
She is a god!
Water Fire!
Touchy, touchy...
Son of a bitch...
And it looks like Liver's got
his hands full with this guy, too.
Well, with all this water
around, I'm sure he should be okay.
But a little backup would be nice.
Not if I can help it!
Aah!
You guys are frickin' crazy if you think I'm
just gonna sit over there and watch the whole time!
You're in the way.
Back off!
You Night Raid people are really freakin' annoying!
Uh!
Hehehe...
Ah!
Huh?
Heh...
Ahh!
Uh!
Damn, this kid is fast!
Hehe...
But I've trained for this.
Akame is faster than you!
What?
Do not compare me to some assassin!
If he hadn't gotten in one lucky
hit, I'd have killed him already!
How's he fighting like this when he's injured?
These Three Beasts are so tough they
make guys like Ogre look like child's play.
Whoa! The fight's starting to
get pretty intense over there!
Of course!
But it's a battle near a body of
water. Sir Liver has the advantage!
Ha! Bro's about to mop the floor with that old geezer.
Liver shall prevail!
He doesn't stand a chance!
The water pressure will destroy you!
Say goodbye, Bulat!
Snake from the Abyss!
Ahhh!
Hehehe...
It seems I correctly assumed you would
attack the snake head-on rather than dodge.
You knew there'd be countless casualties
if I destroyed the ship.
And perhaps, you'd be able to avoid my next
technique if your feet were planted securely on the deck,
but you can't dodge in midair!
Dark Water Spears!
Gah!
Aah!
Takes more than a splash of water
to extinguish the fire in my soul!
But of course.
I would never finish you off with such a simple strike.
After all, I know what you're capable of.
The two of us have been through
many a battle together, remember?
I know all your strengths and weaknesses
better than anyone else in the world.
And that's precisely why I'd like to
show you the power of my trump card!
Water Dragons...
Conquer Heaven!
Gah!
Aaaaah!
Hmm, I think I got him.
Huh?
I can't believe you actually just said that.
You should know better old man!
How did you survive that?!
Haaaa!
Ah!
Huh?
Ha!
Ugh!
What a joke.
You realize what you've done, right?
You just threw away your only chance at defeating Liver.
Bro...
Tatsumi!
I'm sorry, it's my fault.
I wasn't able to
hold him off long enough for you to finish.
What is this? You mean you can still move?
Why don't you just take yourself a little nap,
so I can take my precious time with you later?
Don't sweat it, okay?
Huh?
I'm just amazed you managed to get
through all this without an Imperial Arms.
Uh, yeah, I guess...
Even with his armor, he got beat up pretty bad!
I noticed your Imperial Arms deactivates itself
after you've taken a certain amount of damage.
We seem to have a clear winner.
Hmm. You don't need to play it tough.
That little drop of blood coming
from your ear is a dead giveaway.
Uh?
Your internal organs must've taken a
huge hit when you used your trump card.
So I doubt you're in any condition
to use your Imperial Arms anymore.
Hmph.
Nothing gets past you, does it?
And here I was hoping to have
the upper hand in the negotiations.
Well then! I must ask.
How would you like to become a member of Esdeath's army?
I'm sure she would be willing
to bring you on as a Lieutenant.
Thanks, but I lost interest in
serving the Empire a long time ago.
Don't think of it that way.
You'd be working for Esdeath, not the Empire.
Doing so changed my life for the better.
Since joining forces with Esdeath,
people everywhere cower before me.
In fact, my name is so feared that all the bureaucrats
in the Capital clamour to stay in my good graces!
I've got every single one of them under my thumb!
I implore you to come with me!
If you do, the Master can erase all
of your crimes from the record books!
I said no.
Don't you get it.
I would find no joy in becoming the
very thing we were sworn to destroy.
Since I know Esdeath is scratching the Minister's
back. How could I possibly live with myself.
It'd tarnish my image as a hero
to the masses, now wouldn't it?
A hero to the masses?
I can't believe a known assassin
would dare to say something so arrogant.
I was trying to make it sound like I was being modest.
Both of them have finally reached their limit.
But what they don't know is that
we still have our trump card...
then it's over!
Ah, Bro, wait...
When Imperial Arms users face off...
one of them always dies.
Neither one of us can use our weapons anymore.
Then we'll finish this with our swords.
Ugh.
Huh?
It's time for a little enhancement.
I am about to fight you after all.
Bro. Wait a sec!
Something's not right about this guy!
Yeah, I'm painfully aware he's
not gonna be an easy one to beat.
Here we go!
Ah!
Uh ah!
That's crazy...
it's hard to believe these two are both already injured.
You got him!
My real trump card,
Killer Blood Swords!
Of course you had something up your sleeve!
Keep after him!
Ugh!
Bro, you sure you're gonna be okay?
I don't think I let him land any fatal blows,
so I should be alright.
I put all I had left into that final attack...
and yet you still blocked it. Well played.
If I had hesitated just a second, he would
have annihilated me before I knew what hit me.
When I saw the spray pattern of his blood,
I realized it was another form of liquid.
You were incredible, Bro!
I can't believe he was able to
wipe out two powerful enemies...
even though all I did was get in the way!
Man, that was a really close call!
Bulat...
Huh?
There's one thing I wanted to tell you.
There's a reason I decided to join General Esdeath's army.
I didn't tell you before.
It's a shame to allow a treasure
like you to rot away in a cell.
I'm looking for an adjutant
with incomparable combat abilities.
I'd like you in my army.
Huh?
No, I couldn't return to the army even if I wanted to.
I'm charged with an offense.
Excuses are for the weak.
You may re-enlist...
because I want you to re-enlist.
To put it frankly, I will not
allow anyone to raise an objection.
But the Minister will never stand for it.
I'm a great deal of help to the Minister.
If you're an asset to my forces,
he'll be glad to have you back.
Please say you'll fight with me, Liver.
And if you're still feeling unsure,
allow me to ease your fears.
I have respect and admiration for Esdeath.
That's the real reason.
Liver...
And as such...
I swear on my honor as a devout servant of General Esdeath
that in mere moments I will be taking your life as well!
Hang in there!
Ugh... Uh...
That wasn't just an enhancement.
You injected poison into your own blood!
Uh...
You haven't developed a resistance to it,
so the poison is going to kill you quickly.
It'll soon be over.
As for me...
I must be going on ahead...
I should have expected as much from you.
We have defeated each other.
Bro!
Let's go patch you up!
Tatsumi...
We're not done yet sunshine;
I'm afraid this fight isn't over.
Oh...
Did you really think the Killer
Blood Swords were all we had?
Hm. So sorry.
The real trump card is me.
Trump Card: Invite the Demonic Human.
This weapon is called Scream.
And it can do much more than just make people go to sleep.
Like one little trick is making myself bigger
and stronger, so I can tear your ass to pieces.
Oh, man.
He made himself double in size automatically!
That is one hell of a trump card!
Ah...
Well now, it's been kind of a long time.
It feels pretty good to be back in this body.
This is bad...
He was already too hard to beat.
What the hell am I gonna do now?
Tatsumi...
Uh?
Tatsumi, here.
I'm leaving this to you.
Is that...?
The key to Incursio.
The armor will always belong
to the one who possesses the key.
No, you can't do that! You can't give me Incursio.
What good will it do you if you can't put it on?
Not just anyone can wear that armor.
The wrong person will die
instantly if they even try using it.
You might as well just give it up.
Wouldn't want you to die before we get a chance to play.
So quit being a coward and fight like normal?
Hm...
Huh?
Uhh...
Are you really gonna let your
opponent tell you what to do?
Don't be ridiculous!
Look. You've had a lot of training
and gained some great experience.
That's everything you need to equip Incursio!
Alright?!
I don't know.
Hmm.
I want to avenge my friends by ripping this guy to shreds.
He can't just up and die on me.
You need an affinity for an Imperial Arms.
Yours won't be enough, it'll kill you instantly.
If you like the way a weapon feels...
Or even if you simply have a
positive first impression of it,
you can usually tell if it's a match.
Hyaa!
Whoa, so cool!
I promise you can do this.
You can! I know you can!
Okay, Bro.
Heh.
There's no one in the world I respect more than you.
So if you say I can do it then
there's no way in hell I'll let you down!
Ahh, seriously.
So you're really gonna put it on?
Guess I better hurry if I wanna kill you myself.
Time to die!
Let go and scream, Tatsumi!
With all the fire in your soul!
Incursio!
Amazing...
The armor's changing its shape to fit Tatsumi's physique!
Where'd that thing come from?!
That armor... are all the materials still alive?!
Incursio was created from parts of a living
dragon-type Danger Beast known as "Tyrant."
Its vitality is immensely high.
It can also adapt its body to
survive in any type of environment,
from burning deserts to the frozen tundra!
Even after becoming an Imperial Arms, the
dragon's flesh is still alive to this day!
Such a... such a terrifying weapon!
Tatsumi, your emotions are causing it to evolve.
Incursio's bonding with you!
Esdeath's army committed
Murder-after-murder using Night Raid's name!
Now it's time for you to pay!
Yeah? You must think you're
pretty special now, don't you?!
I can feel it...
this armor is making my body grow stronger.
I'm about to finish this!
Ahhh!
I dare you to try!
Aaah!
Ha, whaddya know?
If that's how strong you are right here and now,
then there's not a single doubt in my mind.
One of these days you will surpass me.
Ugh... Uhh...
Go as far as you can, Tatsumi.
I'll be watching over you.
I won, Bro...
I won because of you.
I'm sorry for that little part at the end...
when I made you punch some sense into me.
I swear, I'll get strong.
I promise, I'll master Incursio and make you proud.
So, just for now...
Is it okay if I cry for you?
Okay, Bro...?
La la la...
Hehe...
Human bodies, they're so amusing. Hehe...
The only way to pluck out the weeds of
rebellion is pull directly from the roots.
Sending supplies to a foreign tribe is a serious crime.
We did what needed to be done.
Kurome, I have a message for you!
You're needed in the Imperial Capital.
Huh?
They only ask for me?
That's right. Apparently you've been personally
selected to be part of a new group of six.
Group of six.
I heard that they were planning on forming a new unit.
Hmmm...
The Capital, huh?
Maybe I'll get to see you again after all...
Big Sister.