Let's make a pact, that when we die, we die together!
We're gonna be leaders in the Imperial Capital!
And make enough money to save
the village! We'll be heroes!
So much for that.
Now I'm out here all alone.
Huh?
Hehehe...
Whoa! Don't sneak up on me like that!
So, have you decided to officially join yet?
I told you guys...
You really do have the makings of an assassin, you know!
It's not a matter of whether or
not I'd be good at it, alright.
I just don't... wanna kill people.
Well, I'm gonna introduce you to the guys anyway!
My neck!
Oh? He still doesn't want to be part of
the team in spite of all that's happened?
He's a bit hesitant.
So I was hoping maybe you could give
him a few words of encouragement, okay?
Hmm...
Well, since we showed you the location of our hideout...
if we can't convince you to
join the team, then you'll be dead.
Uh, is that supposed to be encouragement or a threat?
Just give it plenty of thought, okay?
Huh? "Mend Your Airheaded Ways"?
Oh my god these guys are a bunch of circus freaks.
What the hell?
Hmm?
Leone! Why'd you bring this loser back to the hideout?
He's one of us now.
And did no one think to ask for my opinion?
Uh... Okay.
I won't allow it.
It's obvious you're not cut from the same
professional cloth as the rest of the group.
I mean, just look at you.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Aw, don't let it get to you;
That's Mine's way of saying hello.
Hmph!
This is our practice field
where we go to let off some steam.
Oh! And look who's already out
here trying to work up a sweat.
That's Bulat.
Hyaaaaa!
Incredible. He's really good with that spear.
Oh...
Hey! Oh!
Aren't you the fella we picked up the other day?
Wait, how do you know about that?
Huh? Oh... I should've known you
wouldn't recognize me like this.
I was wearing my armor the first time we met.
Uh... Oh!
Name's Bulat. Pleasure's mine.
Uh... hi there.
And yes he's gay.
Geh! Haha...
Now don't give him the wrong idea...
Yet.
I can think of a lot of wrong ideas.
Hehe... It's almost time for Leone's bath.
I'd do just about anything for a
sneak peek at that smokin' hot body!
In that case...
Huh?
How about you give up two fingers?
You never learn, do you?
Owowowowow!
Next time I'll break your arm.
Owww!
This is Lubbock. As you can see, he's an idiot.
Let's see, who's next?
I don't know how many more I can take.
Hehe. The next one's a cutie, so try not to stare.
She's stuffing her face over there by the fire.
Hey, Akame!
Hm?
And there's this freak!
I'm just now realizing she's eating a giant bird.
Did she kill that thing herself?!
Akame's our resident wild child.
Leone, have some.
Huh? Thanks!
Well? Have you joined us yet?
Uh, no...
Then I'm sorry but I won't be
sharing any of my dinner with you.
I'm okay with that!
This chick's already tried to kill me twice.
I'd better watch out for her.
Is it just me or is everyone
a little extra jacked up today?
That's 'cause the boss is back.
Uh? The boss?
Boss!
Hey!
Welcome back! Did you bring me anything good?
Now why would I do that?
About one of your most recent assignments...
I was told you completed it three days overdue.
Ah, crap!
When facing a powerful opponent,
it's unwise to get caught up in the fun.
Shouldn't you know better than that by now?
Okay, I've learned my lesson, now please let go of me!
Anyway. Tell me about the boy.
Oh! That's right! He's going to be joining us.
I haven't agreed to anything!
Does he seem promising?
Absolutely.
See? All we want you to do is try. 'Kay?
S'not what you said before!
Akame, go get everyone together.
I want to hear about everything, including that boy.
Thank you all. I think I understand the situation here.
Tatsumi! How would you like to
be the newest member of Night Raid?
You're gonna kill me if I refuse to join, right.
No, we won't kill you.
Huh?
But we wouldn't let you leave, either.
You'd have to remain here and work in our factory.
Either way, we won't take your life,
but I do encourage you to join.
Your choice.
I, uh...
I just wanted to make a lot of money in the Imperial
Capital so I'd be able to save my village from starvation.
But the Capital wasn't what I thought.
Tatsumi.
Huh?
Corruption in the Capital is creating
mass-poverty all over the countryside.
Don't you want to uproot all
that corruption at the source?
Like a man would?
Bulat used to be a high-ranking
officer in the Imperial Army,
but he joined us when he realized
what was really going on in the Capital.
If we don't do something about the scum terrorizing
the Capital, then it's never gonna get cleaned up.
So it's our job to take out those
bastards whenever we get the chance.
That's fine...
But I don't think you can make a real big difference by
just eliminating a couple of rotten eggs here and there.
I mean, doing things this way
won't save places like my village.
That's correct. And that's exactly
why Night Raid's the perfect fit for you.
Uh... why is that?
There's an anti-Empire group called the Revolutionary
Army that has a hideout south of the Capital.
A whole army?
They started out small,
but they've grown in to a rather formidable organization.
They needed a separate unit to specialize in covert
operations, such as recon and assassinating targets.
That's why they created Night Raid!
We're only putting out one fire at a time right now...
but when the Revolutionary
Army decides to make its move...
amidst the chaos we'll head
straight for the cause of this mess...
the Minister!
So you're gonna... kill him?
Only then will our nation truly see change.
So if our nation had a new start...
you really think all of the
people would be safe and happy again?
I am certain.
I... I love it.
It's like you guys are taking out the trash...
killing off the bad guys one by one.
You're a rogue team of assassins for the sake of justice!
Huh? What'd I say?! Why's everyone laughing?
Tatsumi, no matter how you describe it,
we're still murderers.
And there's no justice to be
found in the way we do things.
Any given moment...
every one of us could be forced to
atone for the blood that we've spilled.
Man! He has no idea.
It'll be a thousand years before he can handle it.
Hold on.
Uh?
I, uh...
Every team member fights for a different reason,
but each bares a strong resolve.
Are you prepared to risk your life?
You guys are gonna pay me for this, aren't you?
Yes. And if you work hard enough,
I think you'll make more than enough to save your village.
Then I wanna do it!
Please allow me to be part of Night Raid!
You probably won't be going back
to them as some hero, you know.
I know. But that doesn't matter to
me as long as they'll be taken care of.
Hmph.
Works for me.
Prepare yourself for a life unlike any other.
Welcome to Night Raid.
You're dismissed for the night.
Akame...
Hm?
You're in charge of training him for now.
Ugh?
If he becomes a nuisance, feel free to kill him.
No problem.
No problem?!
Better do a good job if you wanna live!
Uh...
It had to be her... I am so dead.
The more skills we can start learning right now
the quicker we'll be able to get ahead in the military!
And if we ever run out of provisions or something,
maybe knowing how to prepare
food might actually save us someday.
Sayo... Ieyasu...
Who knew learning to cook with
you guys would come in so handy?
I said I want seconds!
Oh! Me too!
I'll take some!
Oh yes if you don't mind!
They're running me ragged!
Come on...
I thought I was supposed to become
an assassin, not a stupid chef!
Don't look at me.
I just put food on the plates. M'kay?
Oh, so they won't let you cook because
you kept sampling the food, is that it?
I don't know what you mean.
You are not a very good liar.
Aww, look, you're right at home
in the kitchen, aren't you, rookie?
What?!
Later, Sunshine!
Bulat?
Wait a sec...
are you guys heading out on a mission?
Yeah, this one's a special request.
Shouldn't I come too?
You stay here in the kitchen!
Now you be a good cook and chop a few cucumbers for me.
Why does she always have to be like that?
See ya!
Grrr...
Wow, this place is great!
Today we'll start by catching fish for dinner.
Whoa!
What seems to be the problem?
Thank god it's just a swimsuit.
The target is Koga Tuna.
See how many you can get.
Aren't those things extremely rare
and stupidly hard to get a hold of?
Wha-?
First you have to swim all the way down to the bottom.
Then conceal your aura and make your attack.
You have to act very quickly.
Give it a try.
Hmm... Whatever you say!
Wow. So in the end our little
Tatsumi caught two whole fish, huh?
Akame said you ripped off your shirt
and said some shit like "I got this!"
This'll take some time.
Man... why the hell would she say something like that?
I can't stand her.
Anyway Leone. What did you find out?
Here's the deal. The targets are Ogre of
the Imperial Guard and Gamal the Oil Merchant.
And according to the client...
Ogre has been accepting bribes
from an oil merchant named Gamal.
So whenever he manages to get himself into trouble...
Ogre finds a way to pin all of the blame on someone else.
My fiancé fell victim to this.
And he was sentenced to death.
Please... I'm begging you, you must do something.
Understood. That son of a bitch will get what he deserves.
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Here it is. She paid it all up front.
I'm amazed she could give us that much.
She smelled sickly.
I think she's been selling her body.
Huh? Is that right?
Sure she's not lying?
My senses have never steered me wrong yet, Boss..
He's guilty.
Hmm. Then Night Raid accepts this assignment.
In the new nation we wish to create..
S'no room for his trash.
He needs divine punishment.
We shouldn't have too much trouble with the oil merchant,
but I betcha Ogre'll be a pain in the ass.
Ogre is a demon.
He's very skilled with a sword,
even the hit men are scared of him.
And he's always surrounded by
a huge crowd of subordinates,
he's never seen alone.
He's so careful that Gamal delivers
all payments to his personal chambers.
But on his days off he goes drinking
on Main Street, right by the palace.
Okay. Sounds like we know when we'll have to strike.
But, that area is heavily guarded.
We can't send Akame; They
already know what she looks like.
Hellooo! They don't have any wanted posters of me yet!
Can you do it?
Targets like these pukes are the ones I live for.
I think we should wait 'til the others are here.
But at the moment we still have no
idea when they're coming back, am I right?
Fine! Then I say we set out on this mission without 'em!
Oh? You think you're capable of killing Ogre yourself?
What?
Careful how you answer that!
Keep pretending you're a bigshot
and we might just make you back it up!
Oh!
As you are now, you can't do it.
Wha-?!
But I'm an expert swordsman!
What I mean is that you can't kill people.
Uh... I did it once.
You were blinded by rage that night.
Can you kill a person under any
circumstances without stopping to think about it?
I don't know,
but what if Ogre is framing another innocent person
while the four of us are sitting here arguing about it?!
That's why I don't want us to wait!
I know how much it hurts to
lose someone for no good reason.
And it's not fun!
I don't want anyone else to have to feel like that!
Then it's settled.
I admire your conviction, Tatsumi.
Take him down.
Now that's what I like to
hear! You've got spunk, dontcha?!
I'd like you two ladies to focus on the oil merchant.
You got it!
Understood.
See Akame, I can take care of
business when push comes to shove.
I'll withhold judgement of your ability
until you complete the mission and report back.
If you begin with over-confidence and arrogance...
you'll die.
Uh!
She'll change her tune.
I just have to prove myself by killing Ogre.
This is Main Street.
Did you memorize the map like I told you?
Yeah. Yeah I got it.
If you begin with over-confidence and arrogance...
you'll die.
Tatsumi, I think I should tell
you a few things about Akame's past.
When she was a kid, she and her
sister were sold to the Empire.
They were placed in an assassin
training camp with other abandoned kids.
She learned how to survive the harsh
surroundings as well as the art of murder.
She grew up an assassin, blindly
doing the Empire's dirty work.
But as Akame got older, she started to
see the darkness the Empire was hiding.
One day, she was sent to kill... the Boss.
But it didn't happen.
Somehow, she convinced her to join the Revolutionary Army.
And join the side of the people.
But, by the time she could do it,
most of the kids she had grown up with were already dead.
Do you see what I'm getting at Tatsumi?
Yeah yeah, as a professional killer, you're saying
there are things a rookie like me doesn't understand yet.
Well, if you manage to live through today,
then you'll know a little more.
Whooo! That bathroom will never be the same.
Anyway, time to get back to living the dream!
Wait a second. I've got a better idea.
Killed by two hot babes, you lucky dog!
Now then, I wonder how the newb's
doing with his part of the job?
Ahhh. Nothing like finishing off a long
day of torture than knocking back a cold one.
Excuse me, Master Ogre.
Uh-huh?
I have a matter of utmost importance
I'd like to discuss with you.
That so? Let's hear it.
We need to speak privately.
Huh?
This kid doesn't have an aura.
Alright start talkin'. I wanna get home.
Of course.
Sayo, Ieyasu, please watch over me.
Huh?
Please, sir, I beg you to let me join the Imperial Guard!
I have to earn money to send
back to my family in the country!
Uh... I shoulda known it was something like that.
Follow the procedures like everyone else, jackass.
I tried,
but they wouldn't even take my application.
That's not my problem.
It's not my fault you're a puny little weakling!
That was quick!
He acted without fear.
Been awhile since somebody defied me.
Just like that!
I'll withhold judgement of your ability
until you complete the mission and report back.
Oh! That's right.
I better be getting back to base now.
Huh?
Ah!
Uh!
Did you really think you could slay the mighty Ogre?!
A pathetic little snot-nosed brat like you?
Ugh!
Okay, lemme guess.
You're one of those Night Raid punks that goes
around killing all the people in power, right?
The weak can squeal all they want,
but the strong will always rule in this Empire, boy!
Who you deem worthy means nothing!
I judge the fate of the people!
I won't let you kill anyone else!
On whose order have you come to me, boy?!
The fiancée of the little worm I just had executed?
Guess I was right!
I told myself I shoulda knocked
off that wench while I had the chance!
Well, I still could if I really wanted to.
First thing I'll do is chase that bitch down.
I'll find everyone she knows, bring 'em up on charges
and take my time torturing
them to death while she watches!
But not until I kill you first!
These guys are all the same.
They throw their weight around and
use their power for nothing but evil.
I want nothing more than to take scum like him...
and slash it...
to pieces!
You've defeated a powerful adversary on your own.
I'm impressed.
Yep! Hear that, Akame?
I did exactly what you wanted me to,
And I came out without a scratch on me!
Now, tell me how wonderful I am!
Hmm?
Ah!
What the hell are you doing to me?!
Leone, Boss, grab him.
Ah!
Uh...
Thank goodness.
Oh...
I've seen people die from infection because
they were too proud to report their wounds.
It's good you didn't get hurt.
It's hard for most people to
survive past their first mission.
I'm glad you survived.
Uh... Hm.
The only reason Akame was so hard on you before
was because she was worried about your safety.
Learning to cook helped with your communication.
And hunting taught you basic killing techniques.
Do you not realize everything we made
you do was for a very specific reason?
Oh, uh, I guess not.
Sorry Akame. I got... I got the wrong idea.
It's okay.
Huh?
Just try to keep coming back alive, Tatsumi.
Sure! S'long as you keep looking after me, Akame.
Oh my god this is so adorable and cheesy and the fact
that you're almost naked makes it even more ridiculous.
Hey, you're the ones who took my shirt off!
Well, you're working with Mine on your
next assignment so I expect your best.
Ugh!
Yeouch, out of the frying pan, and into the fire!
Ah!
She's even worse!
I have a bad feeling all of a sudden.