Is this the bandit fort we've been looking for?
Uh-huh!
Our first mission as Jaegers
is to tear this unsightly place apart.
How shall we go about it?
Justice should always be direct.
Strike from the front!
Hm...
Hmm...
So uh, why'd you bring me here?
You're part of the Jaeger reserves.
I suggest you watch and learn for future reference.
Uh! That's the bitch who killed Sheele!
I can't lose my head right now.
Remember what Bro said...
it takes more than passion to survive.
I have to get back to base.
I have to get back and report everything!
Oh...
This could be...
the perfect chance to get away.
Uh...
Mmm...
Oh shit, not anymore!
You're pretty stupid to attack us head-on.
Koro! Phase 5!
Hehe...
Kill them!
Judgement of the Ten Kings!
Devil King's Justice Lance!
Next!
Phase 7!
Cannon of Justice!
Hehehe. All those weapons are my fabulous designs.
The Hands of God, "Perfector", stylishly increases
the wearer's dexterity hundreds of times over!
Oooh, I am just living for this Imperial Arms!
After all the fighting,
I'll get to play with your body parts.
Like precious little dolls.
Ahh!
Uh?
You don't have to thank me for saving your ass.
We're a team y'know.
No. I knew he was there.
Oh yeah, right.
The flamethrower Imperial Arms,
"Invitation to Purgatory Rubicante."
Nothing personal guys, okay?
An angel...
Wing-type Imperial Arms,
"Soaring for Miles, Mastema."
I cannot allow a single one of you to live.
Hmm...
Whoa...
Tatsumi.
Hm?
Soon you'll be able to do that too.
I'm going to train you.
That's awfully generous of you.
I'm not like all the rumors say I am.
To be honest, I haven't been quite myself lately.
I've started to experience love.
And well, it feels good.
Hm...
Maybe this means...
I might be able to convince her to join our side.
Yeah!
I mean...
I could never forgive her for everything she's done,
but if she could change her ways
and help us overthrow the Empire...
Okay, I'll win her over tonight!
Come on, Tatsumi, turn on that manly charm.
Things got hot and heavy a little quicker than I thought!
Uh! Snap out of it, man!!
Okay. Don't freak out.
Just convince her to join the revolution!
Do it. Take control! Take her down like a tomcat!
I must not let her intimidate me!
Sorry for the wait.
No, no it didn't take that long at all!
Can I get you a drink?
Uh, no, no! I think I'm fine.
Hm? You seem a bit nervous.
Huh? No! What, I'm not nervous!
Mm... Aren't you just adorable?
Well, I don't know very much about these feelings either.
It'll all work out if we just let our bodies take over.
Uh... So, I uh...
I wanted to ask you.
Miss Esdeath.
You like me don't you?
If I didn't, then I wouldn't be in this bed with you.
Um... in that case, could you just hear me out real quick?
Hm? Of course, what's on your mind?
To be intimate we must know each other.
It's just, the Empire's kind of a mess right now.
I imagine a lot of citizens
would agree with you about that.
What's your point?
If I'm gonna be doing this kind of work,
I think maybe I should be part of the Revolutionary Army.
And I'd really like it if you
and I could join them together.
Just think of all the lives we could save that way!
Tatsumi.
Uh...
You do realize that you're speaking
to a General in the Imperial Army.
I know this may sound completely ridiculous to you,
but unless things change,
we could end up having to fight each other!
Uh!
There's no need for you to worry about that.
I'll be keeping you by my side forever.
I know you're unsatisfied with the life you once knew.
But with me you'll never need to want for anything.
And I promise I shall be faithful.
I won't even look at another man.
You'll never feel alone again.
Oh...
It's not that I don't appreciate the sentiment,
but I can't.
It's not right if I'm the only one who finds happiness.
So you have a family then?
I can offer them full protection too.
That's not it.
Listen, I want to live in a nation where
everyone can enjoy their ordinary lives.
So, that's why this messed-up
Empire needs to be torn down.
Tatsumi.
Don't you understand?
Of course not! I feel no empathy for the fragile.
"The strong feast upon the flesh of the weak."
That's the law of the land!
Those who die, are not strong enough to survive.
No. There's no way I could fall in
love with anyone who thinks that way!
If you care about me even a little bit,
then please! You have to learn to love life!
That face... I love it...
Tatsumi, that'll never happen.
Understand something.
You're never going to change who I am.
You will be the one changing for me!
That's all there is to it!
You can't expect me to change what I
believe just because you tell me to!
Even if you torture me!
Hm, you're so headstrong.
Perhaps that's why he was able to smile so freely.
I must have his heart.
I must have Tatsumi as my own!
Well, I'm sure you must be tired after today.
We'll discuss it more tomorrow.
For now we should get some sleep.
Ehh...
Okay, I'll be over here on the sofa.
You can sleep in the bed tonight;
I won't do anything to you!
Oh yeah!
Then I should probably take a shower!
Just so you know.
If you wander around the palace or make
any attempt to leave, you will be executed.
Please do not try anything foolish.
Don't worry about me...
That's true,
the guys warned me about how dangerous the palace is.
Ah. I should've had us shower together.
Well, no reason to rush things.
Therefore, not only is he a part of our reserves;
Tatsumi here is also going to be my lover.
Now, if any of you are married or in
a relationship, please raise your hand.
Don't tell me you have a girlfriend!
A lovely wife of six years, actually!
She's such a wonderful woman; I really don't deserve her!
Then maybe you can help me.
What can I do to encourage
Tatsumi to return my affections?
Ooh, the trick is to never giving up!
I'll tell you a secret.
My dear wife turned me down twice before I
found the perfect moment and swept her off her feet!
So bear in mind that it may take some time.
But it will be worth it.
That's very helpful.
Well, I can certainly be determined.
You will fall for me in the end, Tatsumi.
It'll be a fun little game.
Hm?
Hey! How did you sleep last ni-.
Oh wow, you didn't sleep at all.
No, I was so nervous I stayed awake until the sun came up.
She said she wouldn't do anything,
but when I woke up she was spooning me!
You sure do start snacking early in the day, Kurome.
Mind your own business.
You should try to eat more
seafood, it's really good for you.
I wouldn't want to smell like
fish all the time like you do.
What? Really? Do I smell like fish?
Oh, uh, no not really, yeah you kinda do.
Hm?
Something about the way that girl looks...
and her name Kurome,
she just seems familiar somehow.
Uh!
Keep your eyes off of my cookies!
And she's so protective of her food!
Yep, she must be related to Akame!
Gotta problem?
Oh, uh... Please don't be offended, but you really
look like that Akame girl from the wanted posters.
Right! I noticed that earlier too!
Well yeah. I'm related to that goody-two-shoes.
But now she's a traitor to the Empire.
I do hope I run into her again soon.
You know why?
So I can be reunited with my dear sister...
And kill her with my bare hands.
Uh.
Tatsumi! We're off to Fake Mount.
We'll spend the next few days hunting.
Where's Fake-Mount?
You've never been there?
It's in the range beyond the outskirts of the Capital.
We're going to the country!
I can finally escape!
You two will be joining us.
We're hunting Danger Beasts as well as bandits.
Roger that.
Kurome and I will take the east throughout the day.
Wave and Tatsumi, you're in charge of the west.
We'll exchange partners at night.
So Tatsumi will be with me.
Eh?
The monsters that come out at
night are especially vicious.
It'll be my chance to impress him!
I didn't want to say this in front of the
team, but you've got it pretty rough, don't you?
Let me know if you ever need to vent.
Uh, thanks a lot.
But I'll be okay; I mean, I was already
used to being treated like that anyway.
Yeah. Trust me, I understand that.
I just get this weird feeling you
and I are kinda similar, don't you?
Similar? What do the two of us have in common?
Huh? Uh... I'm not sure how to explain it.
It's like we deal with the same problems...
or at least gonna deal with the same problems.
Uh yeah. I totally get it.
We're practically like brothers,
You and I are exactly the same.
Well, let's work together! We
can share each other's pain and-Uh?
Tatsumi?
Uh..
Gah!
Look out!
Whoa! Thanks for that!
No big deal.
I just saved his life without even thinking about it.
But, I should probably get outta here while I still can!
They keep popping up outta nowhere!
And they don't look edible like the ones on the coast.
You ready? Let's wipe these suckers out!
Phew... That wasn't so bad was it?
You finished over there, Tatsumi?
Uh... Tatsumi?
Wha... Where'd he go?
Imperial Arms users probably don't
expect people to get away from them.
But since I have one too, that doesn't really apply to me.
Tatsumi?
Where are you?
Ah! Did he make a break for it?!
Nooooo!
Dammit, dammit, dammit!
I know how you must feel, but I can't let you get away!
I'm too young to die!
I guess it's time.
Grand Chariot!
Maybe this is far enough.
He wouldn't chase me all the way out here, right?
Uh!
Wha... what was that?!
It's an armor type. Just like mine!
Well, how about that?
I can't believe what I'm seeing right now.
That's Incursio, isn't it?
It's the prototype for my armor!
And most importantly...
If you have Incursio, that must
mean you're a member of the Night Raid!
Oh!
Time for a change of plans!
Killing a member of Night Raid is
way more important than finding Tatsumi.
And though my model is newer.
And supposed to have better stats.
I should be cautious anyway.
Is that Wave in there?
Or someone else?
Either way...
I'm screwed if Esdeath shows up!
I gotta get outta here!
Uh!
You're not getting away.
Now man up and fight!
Stop it!
I don't have a reason to fight you!
Yeah maybe you don't...
but I sure as hell have a reason to fight you.
You're Night Raid trash!
I read the file on you guys.
You assassinate people at random.
You threaten the safety of the Imperial Capital.
And worst of all, you're working
with the Revolutionary Army!
Criminals like you shouldn't be allowed to live.
Shut up.
It may be true that we're assassins.
But I am not...
We are not...
We are not the bad guys here!
What's he doing?
Takes more than passion to stay alive, you know!
Oh...
That's right.
No matter what, I have to make it back to
the base so I can tell everyone what I learned!
If you're not gonna come after me,
I'll just have to force the action!
Crap!
Grand Fall!
That was a solid hit!
I'll have to keep track of him.
I can't let him use the water to escape.
Wait, where'd he go?
Aw, crap...
He could be using the current to slip away.
Nice try, but that'll never work on a man of the sea!
Ugh... I didn't have to fight him after all.
I guess Grand Chariot can't go invisible.
Uhh...
Damn.
That last kick was pretty brutal.
Good thing I focused on defense
or that would have killed me.
At least now I think I can finally go home.
Huh?
Woah!
A Danger Beast?!
Shit! Why did you have to show up right now?!
Ugh! This isn't good...
I'm too weak to fight after all that.
This is it!
Uh!
A-Akame?!
Tatsumi. Are you okay?
How did you find me?
We were doing everything we could to keep an eye on you.
Wow, you guys really did that?
All that trouble just for me?
Sorry, guess you ended up saving me again, huh?
Ow!
I'll always be there to save you.
Because you're my friend.
Hm...
Akame...
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm just relieved
to see your face.
Hm...
Welcome back, Tatsumi.
Yeah. Good to be back.
Whooo!
C'mon, we don't have time for sweet talk!
Hurry up, we're going this way!
Thanks for your help back there, Lubb.
Yeah, no sweat. It was kinda my fault
for bringing up that stupid tournament.
If anything happened to you,
then I'd be the only guy left!
Well, maybe that'd be okay, I'd have my own harem!
Man, you're hopeless.
Don't you listen to him;
He was worried sick about you the whole time.
Yeah, I know.
Night Raid...
when I'm with these guys...
it really does feel like home.
Uh, I don't know what else to say.
Except I'm very sorry for what happened, okay?!
General Esdeath, I humbly beg your forgiveness!
Tatsumi got away because you weren't paying attention.
What I cannot overlook, is that a member
of Night Raid slipped through your fingers.
Kurome, more weight!
M-hm.
Ahhh!
Oh my dear Wave.
Your technique is impeccable but it's
worthless if you don't use your head.
Please try to correct this.
Okay...
Oh and next time you disappoint me...
I will be delivering your punishment myself.
Is that perfectly clear?
Yes, ma'am.
Commander! Deepest apologies!
Koro hasn't been able to track him down yet!
Hekatonkeiru is built for combat.
Don't let it upset you.
Where's Dr. Stylish?
We still haven't heard from him.
Well, I'm sure he's found nothing.
Commander.
May I ask a question concerning
the young man you're interested in?
If he did turn out to be an enemy,
then how would you like us to proceed?
Honestly, I still care for Tatsumi very much.
The harder something is to get,
the more desirable it becomes.
However, the lives of my subordinates are more valuable.
I'd prefer if you took him alive, but
I'm giving you permission to kill him.
As you wish, Commander.
Tatsumi's been infected with evil, so
we should just vanquish him right away!
Tatsumi, if they actually manage to
kill you, you aren't much of a man.
But you're stronger than that, aren't you?
You're powerful. A survivor.
I feel it, Tatsumi.
I can't help but believe our paths might cross again.
No, I'll make sure of it.
And when they do, I'll force
you to accept my feelings for you.
I'm coming for you, my love.
And that's everything I found out
about the Jaegers and their weapons.
Gahhh!
So all of those guys can use Imperial Arms?
Man, this blows.
I still can't believe Kurome's one of them.
But when you left the Empire, why
didn't you bring your sister too?
I asked her to come with me.
But she decided to stay behind.
So from Kurome's perspective,
I'm just another traitor who ran from the Empire.
I bet when Zanku showed her that illusion,
it was of Kurome.
Well. Now that you've seen those jerks
up close and personal, what's your opinion?
If we're talking one-on-one,
I don't think any of the Jaegers are tougher than we are.
It's just...
Esdeath.
I've never seen anything like her.
As of now, I really don't think
I stand a chance against her.
Esdeath may have amazing power.
But she still has a weakness.
And what's that?
She's alive.
Her heart is beating as we speak.
Therefore, I can still kill her.
I don't care if she's the
strongest, most evil person on Earth!
Aw, how precious that they tried to
cover their scent and hide their footprints!
But since I brought my super-enhanced
soldiers, it won't do any good.
Hehe... I knew there was
something trig funky about that boy.
You wouldn't expect a blacksmith
to adjust that quickly, am I right?
Bingo!
Peekaboo, Night Raid, I see you.