Kurome...
Unlike you, I chose to be a soldier.
It was my dream.
There was an officer who helped me,
and I wanted to be just like him.
Soldiers fight for what's right.
They're supposed to work hard to
protect their country and their people.
But now that I am a soldier...
I don't...
I don't have any idea what I'm protecting anymore.
Looks like it's down to the four of us.
This place feels really big now.
Yeah, it does.
So, what're we doing after this?
After the revolution's over, there won't
be much work for guys like us, y'know.
If I recall correctly, when I got here you
practically forced me to join the team. Remember that?
And when I did, before I knew
it, everything had gotten all crazy.
Aw, I'm sorry sweetie.
Oh well, then I guess you'll just
have to punish me with a spanking!
No, thank you! Besides, assassins being
out of work means the world is a better place!
I guess so.
Well, maybe we could start a
traveling circus group or something.
Sounds good.
No, it doesn't!
I appreciate all you've done for the cause, team.
Whoa! That sounded way too
much like a final goodbye, Boss!
I don't know whether we'll meet again.
That's completely up to you.
What're you talking about?
You're gonna have a hell of a time
getting rid of these three misfits!
Am I right?!
Of course! You know I'm in!
Good! Then this will be Night Raid's last assignment:
Cut down the source of this corruption,
assassinate Minister Honest!
You have to survive.
I will. You have my word on it.
Tatsumi, your time limit depends on
how long our main forces can hold out.
Kill the minister as fast as you can!
Today we turn our dreams of revolution into reality,
and pave the way for a new world!
By the strength of our hearts, we
will abolish this debauched government,
and its people will finally live in peace!
I'm counting on you.
Bingo! Hardly any guards here, just like we thought.
Lubb's map was exactly right.
Thanks, little man!
Night Raid!
I don't want to kill any more than I have to.
Get out or get ready to die.
We will not retreat!
Shoulda known they would keep the
toughest ones reserved to the palace.
I guess killing them's the only way through.
None of you can cut it against Night Raid.
Please fall back now.
One of the Jaegers.
It's Run.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
I'm surprised you remember me, Tatsumi.
By any chance, you think you could let us pass?
Pretty please?
Oh, sorry. I've always been the type of
person who prefers to finish everything I start.
Yeah? Even if it's a mistake?
History will ultimately decide who made
the right decision in a situation like this.
There's no reason to throw your lives away.
You may leave.
Huh?
You can't help me.
As a matter of fact... you'd be in the way.
Watch out!
Those must be his Imperial Arms!
You were right, y'know.
Just as you thought, the empire, as we
know it, has become rotten to its core.
The current regime is on the verge of collapse.
If you know that, why are you getting in our way?
Because your methods of revolt cause too much bloodshed.
Are you saying you're no different?
Well, you see, I was once a teacher.
How did a teacher wind up in the Jaegers?!
Not long ago, a group of bandits abducted my students
and murdered them.
But the government didn't
treat it like a crime in any way.
Now, the village I came from was quite poor,
so the bureaucrats saw no reason to get involved.
Really? That happened to you?
It did. And it's precisely the
reason I despise this empire.
In that case, why are you not on OUR side?!
That's where you belong!
My plan was to infiltrate the Jaegers.
I thought I'd be able to accomplish more from the inside!
But Night Raid decided to resort to
violence in the name of REVOLUTION!
Man, you piss me off!
I'm gonna knock some sense into your thick skull!
Keep moving, you two. I'll handle this guy on my own!
Sis!
It's not a good idea for us
all to be together in one place!
I'm fine, just GO!
Don't you go dying on me.
Not until I get at least one good
hit on the minister, all right?!
And AS for YOU, this is gonna be over real quick!
It's nothing personal, but your ass was
doomed when you chose to fight for the empire!
You chose the wrong side!
What the hell?!
Divine Wings, my trump card.
You didn't actually expect me to
fight you in hand-to-hand combat?
Oh, crap...
What's the status, Minister?
Doesn't look promising.
I hate to be the bearer of bad news,
but our forces seem to be completely overwhelmed
by the onslaught from the Revolutionary Army.
So we're losing...
I fear our reign's been nothing but failure!
Nonsense! Even in the wake of the
unfortunate passing of your DEAR parents,
Your Majesty has always been steadfast.
And with me guiding your hand,
at what point could you possibly have made any mistakes?
Oh yes, you're absolutely right.
You have been a wonderful example, Minister.
The citizens are losing their minds over a foolish dream!
The revolution they imagine will never come to pass!
It's your duty to teach the defectors a lesson!
I'm sure there will be casualties,
BUT there are times when a leader must make sacrifices!
A display of authority is the
remedy for this absurd rebellion!
Make it so, O Wise One!
Well, well, what do we have here?
It's the rebels!
That man's from Night Raid!
How did you get past the Royal Guards?!
Looks like your precious guards decided to give up.
Minister, you're my target.
You're done!
You're too late!
The ultimate Imperial Arms has been activated!
You lo...
Excuse me...
This empire is coming to an end,
because of what YOU started!
No! Please, listen to me!
Things were messed up far longer than that!
The weak and the poor have been
suffering under this tyranny for ages.
And no matter how hard those people prayed for
things to change, you never did anything to help 'em!
Sayo, Ieyasu, and my friends...
they're all dead now!
This callous nation cannot stand any longer!
Your Majesty, you mustn't
allow him to deceive you! Please!
You hold your tongue, Minister!
Your days of manipulating the emperor are over!
What? You should stop making such
vile accusations in royal company.
I give advice out of love and respect!
That's bullshit and you know it!
Can't you hear what's happening outside?
The capital IS finished!
Careful, boy...
I'd advise you to shut your mouth.
Please, Your Highness!
Crush these traitors in the name of the empire!
Submit before your all-powerful Emperor!
What's happening?!
The empire's secret weapon, Primus Imperator!
A machine that's as colossal and
undefeatable as the gods themselves!
Now the infidels who dared defy
the empire will face its wrath!
Oh God, what is that?!
Oh, no!
What's going on?!
That thing's enormous!
He's using the legendary Imperial Arms!
Hey, wait!
Primus Imperator? So it actually existed?!
Damn that minister!
No wonder he didn't admit defeat.
He had this up his sleeve the whole time!
For generations, our empire has
been a flawless image of divine order.
And anyone who should rebel
against it must atone for their sins!
STOP IT!
Oh, how magnificent you've become, Your Majesty!
Had your mother and father not been taken by
an inexplicable accident, they would be so proud!
Yes...
Only those of royal blood are
capable of using Primus Imperator.
There can be no denying the fact
that you are indeed the chosen emperor!
This is true.
We are rightful heirs to this nation.
Yes, Your Grace! Yes! Yes! Yes!
So this is the weapon Stylish described
as the first and strongest of all Imperial Arms.
This... is for the best.
There's a good lad!
With this power at your disposal, everything
around you is yours to do with as you please!
What's a little destruction
in the quest for absolute power?
The losses can always be purged from the peasants again!
It's just me and the emperor now!
These guys are tough!
But I guess they are the emperor's guards.
Tatsumi?!
Stop! Look what you're doing to your own people!
Night Raid has done this.
This is merely the result of what you've created!
Don't you have any compassion?!
What kind of emperor would be
able to unleash such suffering?!
Silence! This empire is a thousand years old.
We will never allow it to collapse during our reign!
Hear, hear!
Well said, Your Majesty!
The last thousand years have led to this day!
As the ruler of this country,
we were born into a life of crushing responsibilty!
You could never understand how that feels!
It's bigger than you.
It's bigger than all of us.
It's the anguish and agony of everyone around you!
Look! Can't you see it?!
Can't you see what's happening down there!
He lies! Don't listen to such deceit!
If you bow and show leniency,
everything will have been for naught!
It's time to be strong!
Oh... guess that could be what we need.
What're you doing? I never said you could look away!
Your Majesty!
If you have the power to do all this,
why not use it to fight
the real problems out there?!
Shut up.
Are you just gonna be his
little puppet forever, is that it?
SHUT UUUUUP!
Wave?!
I'm an Imperial Soldier.
It's my job to protect people!
Man, am I happy to hear that!
And besides, I already owed you a
favor anyway. Or don't you remember?
Huh? A favor?
Don't worry about it.
Your Majesty, calm yourself! Please!
This crusade is our cause!
We must see it through to the end!
He has to be stopped at all costs.
And you and I are the only ones who can do it!
Yeah, you don't have to tell me!
Infidels! Why do you fight against
your country AND your Emperor?!
Don't try to twist what this is!
It's not like I'm siding with the rebels.
But a soldier is supposed to protect the innocent.
And that's what I'm gonna do!
He sounds like a handful.
Yes, he is.
Hmm?
But we could use more people like him.
We can postpone our little scrap, right, Fly Boy?
That won't be necessary.
Nothing!
Grand Chariot can't even hurt it!
We have to keep fighting!
The second we give in, we lose!
What was that?!
Look out!
That felt different somehow.
No matter how resilient your opponent may
seem, there's always a weak spot somewhere.
Try to remember that next time you're
in battle so you can disarm your enemy.
Su...
Wave! Make me an opening!
Got it!
This traitor must be executed!
For betraying the emperor, you are sentenced to DEATH!
This is the only place that seems worn down!
It's just like you said!
There's gotta be a weak spot somewhere, right, Su?
Nothing's invincible!
DAMN YOU!
Tatsumi!
Just give up!
Why do you have to be so persistent?
We're begging you, please... please surrender!
Don't underestimate me!
I've been through more pain than you can imagine!
I carry the hopes of all my friends who've gone before me,
and I won't allow their deaths to be in vain!
There will always be hardships and misery, Tatsumi.
In fact, that's all we get.
But this is the path we chose for ourselves.
Bro?
We should feel fortunate to do what no one else will.
It's how the world is changed.
And then, we simply disappear.
Bro!
Come on and scream!
With all the fire in your soul!
Yaaahhh...
INCURSIO!
The ancient soul inside the armor is causing it to evolve!
Stay back...
GET AWAY FROM ME!
Yaaahhh!!
Are you trying to get killed?!
Of course I'm not!
I made a promise, didn't I?!
I swore I'd make it back alive!
TATSUMI!
He did it!
I'm sorry.
I guess I broke my promise.
You gave me your word!
Tatsumi... Tatsumi...
Is it over?
Has the empire... fallen?
Have we failed our reign?
Tatsumi...
is dead.