How many intruders and where?
Judging by the reaction of my barrier I'd say about eight.
They're getting a little close
to the hideout if you ask me!
If they were clever enough to sniff us out,
we should assume they're tribal assassins.
Move quickly!
Don't let them leave here alive.
You're still a little new to go
up against a big group like this.
So try to be careful! The first thing is to
let your body get a good feel for the battlefield!
Right!
And the second thing is...
Please call me either "Handsome" or "Bro".
You got it, Bro!
Yeah! Now we're talkin!
Hey, check this out.
Incursio!
Whoa!
Yah!
So cool!
This is the Imperial Arms Incursio.
I don't know what Imperial Arms
are, but, man, that was awesome!
Ah, good, I see you recognize its greatness!
It's them.
Now's your chance to see what Imperial Arms are all about.
Yeah!
That's the girl from the wanted poster.
That means Night Raid must be around here somewhere.
She's a pretty little thing, huh?
Let's not bang her up too bad.
I wanna have some fun with her first.
Huh?
Wha?
Be careful.
You've entered enemy territory, y'know.
Oh, shit!
You bitch!
I'm gonna make you pay for that!
What's going on?
It's poison?!
It only takes one strike.
Crap, they spotted us.
But now I know Night Raid's
hideout is somewhere near here.
That kind of Intel is worth a fortune.
I've got to get back to the base.
Well, he's made it pretty far.
Bummer, I really don't like revealing my location.
You're mine!
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Sheele.
Nice timing! That was just enough danger to power up!
Huh?
Sweet! Bullseye!
The bigger the trouble I'm in,
the more powerful my beautiful Pumpkin becomes!
Hmm?
That sounded like Pumpkin just now.
I'm surprised she puts up with that finicky thing.
When I go into beast mode I can just
beat the living daylights outta my enemies!
Much more fun!
Oooh, it was a lady tugging my strings this whole time.
Please just spare my life!
I'll do anything you want!
Noooo way.
I've seen way too many guys wind
up dead after a girl says that.
Maaan, what a waste.
Why does this job have to be so disappointing sometimes?
Yaaahh!
Look out!
Hyah!
Yah!
He's... so strong!
So this...
this is the power...
of Night Raid.
You still alive, Tatsumi?
Huh?
Uh, yeah!
Then everything's fine!
I can already tell you've got some talent!
Yep!
Night Raid...
They're killers...
But they're bringing about a revolution.
Man, I really have found a crazy group of friends, huh?
Heh!
Why'd I dream of him of all people?!
The Imperial Capital!
There's a giant wall surrounding the whole
city, and the canals are full of trading ships!
There's so much to see!
And don't forget all those sexy, sophisticated city women!
Oooh!
Gross!
Hey, what was that for?!
Sayo... Ieyasu...
I'll do my best for you guys.
I promise.
Hmm?
Is something the matter?
Huh? Oh hey, Sheele.
I'm fine...
I'm supposed to be training with Mine today,
but she hasn't come out of her room yet.
Spoiled little brat.
Yeah, well...
Mine does have a habit of sleeping in.
Seriously?! This is her job!
I'm so sorry for the inconvenience.
I'll go wake her up now.
Wait. Let Tatsumi do it.
What? Why me?
Because you're her subordinate for today.
Waking up your supervisor is part of an assassin's job.
Okay, fine.
I wasn't aware that we had that rule.
Consider it another test.
Huh?
Hey, Mine!
You just gonna sleep all day or...
Hmm?
You coulda killed me!
Well, I missed!
You filthy pervert!
How dare you dodge when you know you deserve to die?!
Oh, whatever! If you hadn't slept in so late,
then I wouldn't have been ordered to come get youuu...
Maybe so, but haven't you ever
heard of a thing called knocking?!
Hey, is there some kind of festival going on?!
She's really going all out.
Tatsumi's in for a long day.
I used to think the capital was great,
but now I can see how miserable the people are.
Hey! Pervert, hurry up!
What's the hold-up, country boy?
Let's move it! Chop chop!
Aren't you supposed to be my faithful servant for the day?
Servant?!
That's what the boss said.
No, I'm just training under you.
There IS a difference, you know!
Yeah, and the operative word there is "under".
C'mon, we don't have a lot of time!
Wha-Hey, wait!
Hmph!
Hey, Mine?
What?
Don't these people look unhappy to you?
They live in fear of the
government. and the economy sucks.
Most everyone's either at rock
bottom or on their way down.
You wouldn't be that chipper either.
Go ahead and cry. Nobody's listenin'!
Hey, what do you two think your do-.
Shouldn't you two jerks be
picking on someone your own size?
You gonna do something about it?
It's fine. This little girl's a
refugee from outside the country.
I mean, she could turn out to be a traitor any second.
So could I.
Huh?
Tatsumi?
Got it.
Hmph.
Thank you for saving me.
Don't thank me.
Just grow up strong so you can protect yourself, okay?
Ah...
I hate to ask, but is it safe for you to
wander around in broad daylight like this?
Huh? Why not?
They've only identified four of us so far.
Guess that makes sense.
Huh?
Wait, who's that guy in the middle?
That's Bulat.
Ohhh, Bulat.
Tha... that's bro?!
That picture's from back in his army days.
He changed his look whenever he signed with Night Raid.
That looks nothing like him!
Ah, hah.
Oh man, that's all I need is
another image to haunt me in my dreams.
Anyway the Boss gave this mission to you
and me, because we can walk around freely.
Understand?
Oh, okay!
I was wondering why we were patrolling this part of town.
Good! Now it's time for our retail investigation!
I don't know what that means, but woohoo!
Ahhhh... What a day!
Nothing makes me happier than a brand new pink dress!
Yeah, whatever...
Isn't it wonderful to have a whole day to goof off?
Well, the mission's complete!
What the hell?! We did nothing but shop all day!
Welp, Get over it!
Have you already forgotten that I'm above you?
Good servants don't question their masters.
You should be grateful that I deemed
you worthy enough to carry my bags!
Yeah well you're not gonna be my boss forever, you know!
Plus, nothing we did counts as training!
What? You think you can just
waltz in here and be on my level?
You do seem pretty confident
in your skills as a swordsman...
but you haven't seen nearly as much combat as me.
I get it.
Huh?
I'm new...
So there are going to be some things
about this job that I don't get yet.
But still! I am gonna keep on fighting!
For Sayo and Ieyasu!
Ah...
Akame and Bulat have high hopes for you,
but I have my doubts.
So what's that all about?
It's an execution.
They're pretty common here.
How can they do this to people?
It's the minister who supports this sort of cruelty.
Ultimately, he put the child emperor
on the throne so he could be in control.
As for me...
I'll never end up like this.
I am going to survive this hell no matter what happens!
The Minister, huh?
What kind of monster is this guy?
Administrator Shoi...
For speaking out publicly against Our
policies and interfering with matters of state,
We decree you shall be drawn-and-quartered!
Did We make the right decision, Minister?
Oh yes, Your Highness.
You're the wisest ruler the Empire could ever dream of.
Is that meat again?
You eat that a lot.
I want to enjoy it now, while I'm young and healthy.
Buono, buono!
Your Majesty, the minister is deceiving you!
Please! I implore you! Open your
ears and hear the voice of the people!
Well, Minister, did you hear what he just said?
Seems the poor fellow's lost his mind.
Right! You've never lead me astray
before, so this man must be insane!
My old friend...
Why must it end this way?
No, please! Your Grace if you don't
stop him, he'll lead the empire into ruin!
Please... Your Grace.
No need to worry.
You can count on me to look after that
beautiful wife you're leaving behind.
I'll be sure to satisfy all her needs.
And I do mean "all" of them.
Nooo! You can't let this happen!
He can't do this!
He must be stopped!
Someone... anyone...
I'm begging you... That man is a demon!
Can't any of you see that?!
Please! Pleeeaaase!!!!
Night Raid has a new mission.
This time our target is a distant
relative of Minister Honest: Iokal.
He's been using the minister's name so that he can
kidnap innocent women and then beat them to death.
Iokal also has five mercenary guards.
They're equally guilty.
I'm counting on you guys.
Now, go take him out!
So that's Iokal's mansion.
It's enormous.
Hey, Mine.
What?
Is that one of those Imperial Arms things too?
Yep! Its name is Pumpkin.
It gets more deadly the more danger I find myself in.
But a girl like me is hardly ever in any real danger.
How on earth did you figure out
how to make something like that?
Nobody makes Imperial Arms, stupid.
Jeez, they're ancient, legendary weapons.
I'm amazed by the things you don't know.
I don't need a risk factor this far away.
I'll shoot him as soon as he sets foot outside.
Right, and as soon as you splatter him, it's my
job to make sure you don't get hurt on the way back!
Leave it to me!
Heh! I'll keep my expectations low.
She's so determined...
I can almost feel how focused she is!
Here he comes.
Where?
Ah! Okay, I see him, but those
other guys aren't on the hit list!
That's fine.
How is that fine?
You'll never make the shot from here.
They are irrelevant.
Irrelevant?
No, don't!
We can't shoot innocent pe-.
Oh, I should let you know, I'm
kind of a badass, sniper genius.
We must find Lord Iokal's killer at all costs!
If we don't, the minister will have our heads!
Right! He can't be too far!
What do we have here?
Nice of you guys to save us
the trouble of chasin' you down.
Ah, man! The escape route is not ideal.
Think they've finished off the guards yet?
Those guards trained at the Imperial Fist Temple.
It may take a little while.
That's the best martial arts temple in the Empire.
Guess you get what's coming to you
if you mess with the minister's family.
Yeah. He was using his family's influence to get ahead.
I hate that more than anything!
Sounds like there's a story there.
I feel like being nice to you right now,
so I'll tell you the story behind that.
Didn't even have to ask!
I was born into one of the tribes on the western border.
That means half of my blood is foreign.
The villagers treated me terribly because of it,
and no one showed me an ounce of respect.
My childhood was a nightmare.
But the Revolutionary Army formed
an alliance with the western tribe.
So if we do end up having a new nation,
people will stop caring about our differences!
And no more kids will have to
go through what I did growing up.
I will not allow anybody else
to ever suffer such intolerance!
Wow, Mine...
Not to mention after everything I've
accomplished in the name of revolution,
I'll get loads of reward money
and grow old in the lap of luxury!
Oh man, that felt so incredible!
That was a rather pleasant challenge, wasn't it?
Something's not right.
I thought the Boss said we were supposed to kill five.
Aw man, I didn't get to kill anybody!
So I guess there's one left.
Too bad, Lubb.
I'm dockin' your pay.
What?! You can't do that!
Wanna bet?
Tatsumi...
This is the rendezvous point.
Guess we're all done.
Not until we report back in, remember?
Ha! You sound like Akame.
Look out!
Tatsumi!
Who are you?
I must say I've outdone myself.
You're a fighter from the temple.
I am. Assistant instructor, to be exact.
Course, that was ten years ago now.
And look at you now, protecting a nobody!
Oh my, how far the mighty have fallen!
Let's just say I stirred up some trouble!
Better say your prayers, little girl.
You're going straight to the minister!
That's not gonna happen!
Hurry, Mine! Shoot him!
Tatsumi...
I can't believe you'd sacrifice yourself!
I'm still alive, you know!
You said you're a genius sniper, didn't you?
You can do it!
Damn it, put me down right now!
Hurry!
Since when do you think you can give me orders?
Might as well give it my best shot though!
Ah crap!
You... You bastards are gonna pay dearly for...
for assassinating... a member
of the minister's own family...
Hey, you. Looks like you've got some guts after all.
I suppose I ought to commend you on your braver-.
You didn't need to cut it that close.
Look at what that Pumpkin thing did to my freakin' hair!
Ah! What's with you?!
A genius was about to give you a compliment, dumbass!
Oh, shut it! You're not a genius,
you're just too smart for you own good!
I guess there was no need to rush
all the way over here, was there?
Some fellow Imperial Arms users...
and they're killers!
Mmm, how utterly delightful!
I must get my hands on them.
Hey, you over there!
What're you doing back here?
Don't move!
I think the Imperial Capital's going to
be the perfect place to call my new home.
It's so crowded there's a new victim around every corner!
How delightful!