I don't get it. I feel like we've looked everywhere.
Where could their hideout be?!
Well, Kyoroku is an extremely large city.
And since this religious organization is a fairly peaceful
one, we can't do anything drastic to lure them out.
It's going to take more than simply attacking someone.
Here!
Kids are so cute!
They're still so young and pure,
they haven't been tainted with evil!
Wow, I never realized she could actually smile like that.
Yeah, she'd been stressed for quite a while.
So Esdeath told her she should
try a little change of pace.
By the way, you've been hanging around a lot lately.
Have you decided to join us or what?
Hmm... I guess we're "partners."
Whatever it takes to get General
Esdeath to put me in my place.
I'm not sure why,
but something about this girl reminds me of Dr. Stylish.
See ya! Remember to have fun playing
and never cheat. Okay, boys and girls?
Okay!
It's so nice to guide them down the path of
righteousness while they're young and impressionable!
Yes, this is what is right. This is my country!
I'll protect it at all costs.
That's all the info the spies gathered.
We will launch the plan the day
of the Path of Peace celebration.
Wow, going out with a bang, huh!
During the festival,
we'll slip through the crowds and sneak into the palace.
Then we'll go in for the kill!
Serves him right.
This job will send the Revolutionary Army into action!
Failure is not an option!
Dinnertime, everyone.
I pulled out all the stops today.
Is everyone ready to have their minds blown?!
Yeah!
Najenda gets ramen. The noodles are extra firm
and the balance of chicken and salt is just right!
Mine gets strawberry parfait.
I even added a little something extra.
And for Lubbuck, I've prepared a fresh Bohai shrimp.
Leone gets oden and assorted local brands of sake!
For Akame, I have a collection of meats
from every beast I could find in the forest.
And Tatsumi said he's not picky so he gets, well... this.
Huh?
But this looks like it's for little kids!
As a special treat, I had Susanoo
cook up everyone's favorite food.
So go ahead and chow down; You're going to need energy.
Oh, no need to tell you twice.
I'm glad everyone's hungry.
Mmm! So sweet! I love it!
Tatsumi, you gotta try a bite of this.
Tatsumi, you do know what you're s'posed to
do when my cup starts getting empty, don't 'cha?
Yeah, yeah, okay, I'll pour you some more.
That's right; You're such a good boy!
Good God! You ate all that?!
Another amazing meal. Thank you, Su!
Yeah! Seriously, I don't know what we'd do without you.
You're awesome!
I'm deeply honored to know I've pleased you.
But, Tatsumi...
You didn't eat the last grain of rice.
I don't know if I can stand it.
Sure is a shame. This guy would be perfect
if he wasn't such a ninny all the time.
If Night Raid plans to strike, it'll be today.
But that goes without saying, doesn't it, Seryu?
Suzuka, do not let those demons into the cathedral, okay?
Yeah, I know.
That girl's got combat experience.
I can tell by those eyes and the way she walks.
Damn! Didn't take 'em very long to spot us.
They won't chase us all the way out here.
Yeah, well, we had to get out of the city.
I hope we created a good enough distraction.
All we can do now is cross our fingers and
pray the boss and everyone else pulls through.
It feels like I still have makeup all over me. Ugh...
Did I get all of it off?
Y-yeah... yeah, I think so!
Why are you getting all red?
You're not taking all that
"string-of-fate" crap seriously, are you?!
Oh, you wish! But it sounds like YOU‘’ve been
thinking about it since you're bringing it up!
Ugh, shut up!
Don't be ridiculous! If you're my "soulmate",
then explain why you didn't try to save me
when I almost got eaten by that giant frog thing!
Where were ya on that one?!
Hey now, I kinda had my hands full, remember?!
There's that Night Raid girl I fought before.
So why in God's name is Tatsumi
with her? What in the hell?
He's been corrupted by evil.
Koro, Phase 9!
Justice City Detector!
There aren't any civilians in the area.
At last, destiny has reunited us once again, Night Raid!
Koro and I will erase your kind,
with the swinging Hammer of Justice!
Koro!
I'll give them a taste of my explosive weapon
that combines Judgement of the Ten Kings 2, 7, and 8!
The great commander showered you with
affection and you repay her with betrayal.
And now, you return with the girl whose
partner hacked off my arms and tried to kill me!
You shall be punished by fire for your sins!
I smell gunpowder!
Justice...
VOLLEY!!
They survived that?
Stubborn little devils!
They certainly seem to be after us.
Right? If you ask me, they're trying to
keep us as far away from the town as possible.
Must've struck a nerve.
Here comes another round! Get ready!
The attacks have slowed down,
so I guess we're out of range.
I got a look at the shooter.
It's definitely Seryu Ubiquitous.
Seryu Ubiquitous, huh?
Which way is that bitch shooting from?
It's the fourth Rakshasa Demon!
Suzuka. But I don't suppose it makes much difference
what you call me since you're about to be dead.
Oh, really now!
Get outta here, Mine!
I don't think so! After what she said,
there's no way I could just- Ah! Tatsumi!
There's been a change of plans.
You get to fight me instead!
Oh, aren't you brave?
All right, I'll let you be the
first to die. How does that sound?
Tatsumi!
Stupid.
Okay, you take care of her...
And I'll deal with Seryu.
After I finish my business with
her, I'll come back to help you.
Koro, Phase 6!
Woof!
What's that?! Does she ever run out of stuff?!
The rebellion will never find peace!
Those with no value for justice will meet their end!
Thanks for the big target.
What?! She took down my most powerful
attack with a single shot! Fine!
Koro, Phase 1!
I came here to personally ensure
the condemnation of Night Raid.
So, we finally meet again.
Koro's gonna eat your corpse,
just like he did your two friends.
TWO friends?
We put a woman's head on display in the
middle of Romaly, a redhead I do believe.
And Koro ate the rest of her!
The same with that purple freak in the glasses.
They both ended up in a little pile on the back lawn.
And now it's your turn!
You know, you like to consider
yourself a fighter for justice,
but you blindly followed Ogre and Stylish.
You never even stopped to think
about how messed up they were, did you?
But then again, so are you.
You laugh exactly how those two sick freaks used to laugh.
You're just like them.
That's why I have absolutely no problem taking your life.
I'm gonna put a hole through you!
Do you feel better getting all that off your chest?
Koro, Phase 5.
Don't forget the arms.
All you managed to do was give
Koro enough time to regenerate.
The evil of this world are so stupid.
Let's go, Koro!
How is it so powerful?!
Maybe because I've been holding back.
This fight'll be more entertaining
if it's a true two-on-one!
The best thing about Pumpkin is it fires
with more power if I find myself in a tight spot!
Don't give up, Koro!
She can't possibly keep up a surge like that forever!
Maybe not! But thanks to our last battle,
I've almost figured out where the core is!
I don't need much more time! And then it's over.
Damn you! Koro, use your trump card!
I'm prepared for this.
I've seen everything this Imperial Arms can do!
Devil King's Justice Lance!
She's more dangerous now.
Her personal weapon's not an
Imperial Arms, but it's really strong!
I'll BEAT YOU TO DEATH!
I took on too much damage.
Shit, I should've just finished her off.
This girl is really freakin' fast.
She's all over the place.
Aw, you made me break a nail.
Son of a...
Killing Mez, that was one thing,
but I was surprised one of you took out Ibara.
Though it clearly couldn't have been you.
It's painfully obvious how
little combat experience you have.
Once again, I'm not strong enough.
I've dealt with this regret too many times.
Over and over and over!
No matter how tough she is, I cannot let it happen again.
Are you back at a hundred percent now, Koro?
Good. It's time to destroy this demon once and for all.
Natara! Doya!
Oh, hey Su! How are things going?
So far, so good.
We just need to stick to the plan and lure the enemy here.
You must understand, I don't
have time to play around with you!
Now where's my big sister?
Oh, you wanna know? Okay, but before I tell
you, you're gonna pay for cutting off my arm!
I'm still not healed from the last fight.
Say your prayers, kid!
Stop picking on her...
and fight me.
Sorry I'm late, Kurome.
What? Do you want Su to send your ass flying again?
Come and get me, Night Raid.
I'm not gonna let you hurt my teammates anymore!
Grand Chariot!
General Esdeath, I need the Jaegers; Where are they?!
Shut up. You're getting just what you deserve, Bolic.
If you'd listened, you wouldn't be in this mess.
You must protect me!
The minister himself commanded you to...
You're right, orders are orders.
I will continue to keep you safe.
However, I must forbid you to leave this room.
Yes! Of course!
If your plan was to lose me in the ruins, it won't work.
You'll just tire yourself out
and make your death too easy.
Yeah? Well sorry,
but you're going down one way or another!
Get ready to join your little friends!
What the hell? This guy's gonna kill us both.
You're not getting away!
This is your end!
This... This brings back some memories.
How they called me a half-breed
while they trampled me in the street...
I just kept gazing into the sky.
No one ever stopped. No one ever helped.
Then, I realized...
the only one who could save me...
was me.
I made a promise to myself that I would
never live such dark days ever again.
And I would never let anyone
else suffer such discrimination.
Which is why...
I will not die here in the middle of nowhere!
Now!
I'll have my revenge!
Koro!
The Ten Kings are out of
ammunition, but I still have these!
Justice must prevail!
This is it!
No! How could I let this happen?
My weapon creates power out of emotional energy.
The more intense my feelings, the more fuel for Pumpkin.
So the moment you pissed me off...
that was when you lost.
Justice will always prevail.
No matter what the cost, all evil must be cast out.
Judgement of Ten Kings.
Final Phase: Godotenrin's Furnace.
You've got one minute.
What the hell?! You bitch!
The doctor was kind enough to give it to me,
the ultimate weapon against sin!
As long as it lives inside my
head, I can never truly lose!
Damn you!
Oh no, it's overheated!
You're too weak to get away!
You're not gonna make it!
You'll burn like the demon you are!
Koro...
You can't heal yourself anymore.
It's not fair; There's still
so much evil left in the world.
I can't die until it's gone.
Not yet...
Shit, my... my legs!
I cannot accept this.
If I die, how will I ever
fulfill my promise I made to myself!
And I have to keep living for
the sake of Sheele and Chelsea!
Why would I suddenly think of everyone?
I can't leave them alone; They wouldn't
have a clue how to do anything without me.
Here it comes!
I was too weak when we lost Bro.
And I was too slow when we lost Chelsea.
But that's it.
I will not lose anyone else.
Tatsumi...
Looks like you'll be okay.
Oh yeah, I did exactly what you told me to do.
You said I should be there to help
out whenever you're in trouble, right?
So that's what I did. How about that?
Your bullcrap actually made an impression on me.
Y'know, Tatsumi? You can be a real patronizing asshole.
But...
I really do appreciate it.
Thanks a lot.
Uh... yeah, sure.
Bolic!
Where is that pig?
He already ran away.
Najenda...
It seems he didn't take your advice.
I'm sure my subordinates are silencing him as we speak.
Nice try.
Horimaca!
But it barely even scratched me!
You always did come up with clever little schemes.
Oh, yes. I like to think I have a better
understanding of your talent than anyone.
So I wouldn't be so foolish as to try to take you head-on.
I guess the fight's over for now, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, Tatsumi.
Hmm? What's up?
As soon as this is all behind us,
I need to tell you something.
Can't you just tell me now?
No, I can't.
Wha... Why not?
I'm feeling so confused, so conflicted.
I never imagined I'd want to
live for someone besides myself.
Promise me something.
Promise me you'll survive.
Yeah, of course I will.
If these feelings are driving me,
then I should be able to tap into some
powers far beyond any I ever have before.
From now on, my battles will be even more intense.