Yes...
Perfect! It's all better!
It was nice taking it easy waiting for my arm to heal,
but I'm ready to fight again!
With Sheele and Bulat gone, I'll have to work extra hard!
Okay! Which one of you is gonna train with me?!
Hey, Mine! What's up?
I'm glad your arm's feeling better.
What are you guys doing?
These pansies weren't getting anywhere
with their training, so we decided to help out.
I never realized...
until I actually put on Incursio, how
fast that thing can take a toll on my stamina.
If I wanna wear it for long battles like Bro did,
I'm gonna have to bulk up.
With the way I am right now,
I can only go invisible for about a second.
It's a bit unusual to see you getting all sweaty, Lubb.
Well since the team is down to only two guys now,
figure it's about time I started
getting a little bit more serious.
It's cute when you talk all big,
since you haven't done half
as many pushups as Tatsumi here.
But it's not his fault.
There's a considerable weight
difference between me and Leone.
Good, you're all here.
Boss!
I'm off to the Revolutionaries' main base.
I'm thinking they'll need the
weapons we got from the Three Beasts.
By yourself?
And you're taking that battle axe? Isn't it kinda heavy?
Nah, I can handle it. See?
Now there's no way I could actually use it,
but I can at least lug it around.
I had no idea she was such a badass.
Of course she's a badass. She used to be a general, man.
Akame, I'm leaving you in charge.
I want everyone to buckle down and train hard.
Okay, whatever.
Hey! Could you be serious?!
Ah, don't worry too much, Akame
always gets the job done either way.
I'm also going to the base to try and
recruit a couple new members for the team.
Although, I highly doubt they can afford to give
us anybody who's ready for combat at the moment.
I'm sorry, guys. I'm trying to get better, I promise.
The Three Beasts you defeated on the cruise ship...
They were at the center of the Empire's
offensive forces and members of Esdeath's army.
But you and Bulat managed to defeat them.
Esdeath may be a powerful foe, but
she's suffered a devastating loss.
When the revolution begins, we will
have considerably less to worry about.
You didn't just save passengers.
You ultimately saved thousands of revolutionaries
who will be needed in our struggle against the empire.
You are strong, Tatsumi. And you're doing a great job.
Yes, ma'am.
I didn't tell you before, because
I didn't want it to go to your head.
But Bulat told me something.
Tatsumi's still got a lot to figure out,
but I can see he has amazing potential.
If we do a good job training him, maybe he could
even improve enough to surpass me one of these days.
I can't wait to see what he does.
Thanks, man!
Take pride in yourself, and survive.
That's all you can do.
Try your best to become the kind
of person Bulat wanted you to be.
Our need for more members is critical.
Leone's report that Esdeath is forming a special
unit entirely of Imperial Arms users is disconcerting.
I have to do something.
Liver, Nyau, Daidara...
All three of you were killed.
I suppose that means you were just too weak.
You've fallen victim to the laws of natural selection.
Such incompetence.
I cannot change the past,
but I promise I shall avenge your death.
The replacements will be arriving today.
The word is they're a smattering of eccentrics.
Might as well have some fun.
My name's Wave.
I served in the Imperial Navy. I'm a man of the sea.
I'm here because I got promoted
to the special police force!
It's my first day in the capital, so I'm kinda nervous.
But not to worry! I'm wearing this awesome cool outfit, so
I'll be in with the locals. It was a huge hit back home.
Yeah! I'm gonna fit in just fine.
He's stinky!
Totally!
Besides, Mom even gave me some of our
highest-quality fish to share with my new friends.
People'll be offended if ya got nothin' to offer, hon!
But I dunno...
What's with him?
Frickin' redneck.
I could be imagining things, but I
feel like everybody's staring at me.
Maybe city people have different rules of etiquette.
Oh well!
If I can handle fighting pirates and
aquatic Danger Beasts, then this is nothing!
There's no reason to stir things up!
Okay! My future teammates are waiting behind this door.
First impressions are everything!
I have to show I mean business.
Don't let 'em walk all over ya! Let 'em know who's boss.
Greetings, friends! I'm here from the Imperial Navy...?
I'm so sorry!
Oh God, that was probably the interrogation room!
Man, I'm such an idiot.
You're kidding!
I'm gonna be working with that guy?!
Uh... hello again!
I should probably do my best not to piss this guy off.
Oh, crap, what'd I do?!
Why is that freak still staring at me like that?!
Oh, no... Mom, please don't
be ashamed if I come back home!
It's a normal person!
Uh, hi!
Nice to meet you, my name's Wa-Heeey!
Stay away from my cookies.
Never mind! Not normal.
I'm sorry I bothered you.
Damn, these guys are wack-jobs!
Hello, comrades!
I'm Seryu Ubiquitous,
member of the Imperial Guard!
And my friend's name is Koro!
She's probably not that crazy, right?
Please come grace us with your presence, Dr. Stylish!
Ah, I love a good dramatic introduction.
The very definition of "stylish".
You've captured my masculine grace.
Oh great, now there's this guy?!
Oh my, you're just a little country boy!
You're just too adorable by far?!
I'll polish you up in no time, cowboy.
So don't be shy.
I think he likes me...
Good afternoon.
Oh, it would appear that I'm the last one to arrive.
Huh? Oh yeah, nice to meet you. My name's Wave.
Hello there. Call me Run, the pleasure's all mine.
Yes! There is a person here who doesn't freak me out!
Uh... excuse me.
T.. The tea is ready, if anyone would like some.
S-Sorry.
I would have said hello before,
but I'm a little bit... shy.
Y'know, bashful. Sorry, I... I'm sorry.
Whoo, looks like I'm the oldest one here.
I really need to get my act together, don't I?
I-I hope we all get to be close friends.
Call me Bols, from the Incendiary Squad. Please.
Didn't peg him for the shy type.
The Incendiary Squad...
That's the stylish unit that will
incinerate anything, even living people.
Explains his interesting look...
but he is not my type.
And who might you be?
What in the hell are you all doing in here?!
What's your problem?
We were all invited to come and...
You never know who's an assassin.
Don't ever let your guard down.
This one has good reaction speed.
You can't attack from behind when
your bloodlust is so easily sensed.
I'm not gonna hold back, even if this is just a game.
Must be the Imperial Arms Yat-su-fu-sa.
Just as sharp as expected.
General Esdeath!
God...
So... even the superior officer's a nutcase!
I hope you found that enjoyable.
I didn't want to bore anyone with a formal meet n' greet.
Nah, I'm used to a little rough-housing.
Your advice was very helpful! Thanks a lot!
Good. After we visit the
Emperor, we'll have a little party.
Wha?! We're gonna meet the Emperor?!
With all due respect, aren't we
taking things a bit too quickly?
I prefer to get the more tedious things over with first.
Oh, by the way, General...
Have you decided on a super-fierce name for the squad yet?
Yes.
We are an independently mobile team charged with
hunting down an elusive gang of vicious murderers.
Therefore...
I'd like us to be called...
the Jaegers.
I love the idea of all of us eating together,
especially since the meal is
the seafood I brought for everyone.
But why are we the only ones who know how to cook?
Wave!
The spinach goes in last.
It'll wither if you put it in too soon.
Uh, you're right. I'm sorry.
Anyway, I wanted to tell you...
It's a huge relief to find out
you're such a nice guy, Bols.
N-No, I'm afraid I'm not all that nice.
Commander?
Yes?
When you're not working, what sort of
things do you like to do in your free time?
Torturing prisoners... Learning new methods of torture...
But as of just recently...
I've found... an interest in love.
Love?
Anyway, I've heard reports that
we have an extra Imperial Arms.
Oh! Uh, yes!
It's a scissor-type weapon
that I have reclaimed from evil!
But we have yet to find anyone who can use it.
The minister will confiscate
it if we don't find a wielder.
Which would be a waste.
To make things interesting, we'll
turn our search into a little game.
Yo!
Hey!
Come on in!
After you.
Whoa...
This really is like a secret base.
Yup! It's my pride and joy.
Come on, it's not like you built the place yourself.
Hel-looooo! Welcome to our Imperial Secret Base!
You're not being very secretive!
Well, the Imperial Guard's put up wanted
posters of some of us all over the city.
But there are still a few of us
who can still be seen out there.
Yeah, and if that isn't enough for ya,
the whole capital's been going crazy. Some
kind of special police force called the "Jaegers".
That's because Esdeath is in charge of it.
She's a pretty big deal in this town.
You don't wanna mess with her.
Is this Esdeath chick really all that dangerous?
You have no idea.
Okay, maybe I should tell you the story.
So, several years ago...
A southwestern tribe raised the standard
of revolt against the cruelty of the empire.
So the empire sent the army to quiet them down.
The tribe only had 10,000 men as
opposed to the Imperial Army's 120,000,
so it seemed like the outcome would be clear.
But it turned out to be way more complicated than that.
Since the Imperial soldiers were
so used to their cush city life,
they weren't able to survive in the harsh wilderness.
Plus, the tribesmen would attack at night,
so that made it even more difficult for them.
The Empire started to panic, so they
dispatched General Najenda and General Esdeath,
who were already extremely
talented despite being so young.
You seem to be in a bad mood, General Esdeath.
Can you blame me?
The minister ordered me to use
Imperial Arms to exterminate the rebels.
I'd hoped to take my time punishing the
forces who wiped out the Suppression Unit,
but he doesn't share my interests.
It takes all the fun out of the whole thing.
But what can you do?
No matter if it's Danger Beasts, killer insects,
plagues or viruses...
Anything that gets in my way... will freeze!
Her power... it's incredible.
We'll take over the enemy base, okay?
Man, I feel like a cannonball when I charge like this!
Artillery... fire!
As soon as you slaughter them, you can enjoy your reward!
Have your way with this wretched city!
It's beautiful, isn't it? Your
precious home burning to the ground.
You bitch! Just finish me off!
I feel like being merciful. I think I'll take pity on you.
I'll allow you and your friends to go free.
Like hell you will!
If you don't just kill me, I swear
you're gonna wish you'd never come to this...
Listen well.
Such is the fate that befalls those who are weak.
Don't like it? Make yourself strong.
What do I do? There's no way I could
obey an order to slaughter those people,
nor can I stand with those so ready to do so!
Well, that's the story.
It's pretty sick how she drilled hate
into those people before letting them go.
Hang on though, from the empire's side,
seems like she was instigating the rebellion.
Yep, that's exactly what Esdeath was trying to do.
She wanted to stir up another uprising.
That way she could get her
kicks on the battlefield forever.
She sounds like a lunatic!
That was a close one.
I made the right choice when I
didn't pick a fight with her by myself.
I mean, you would have to murder like
millions of people to get a reputation like hers.
The way you guys are talking
about her, she must be a monster!
You can check her out for yourself if you want.
She's sponsoring a martial arts tournament.
There's a cash prize for the winner.
So you could earn some money for
your village while you're at it.
Uh, Minister...
Why do you think General Esdeath is so
interested in falling in love all of a sudden?
Everyone begins to have these
feelings once they reach a certain age.
General Esdeath was born to fight.
She has cared for nothing but war.
Now, she's awakening to her carnal desires.
Interesting.
It would be wonderful to locate a match for her.
She's an incredibly prideful woman.
She won't waste any time on a
suitor who doesn't meet her criteria.
But how will we ever find a man like this?
Number One: Above all else, he must have potential.
I'd like to personally train him to become a general.
Number Two: He must have composure
and be able to hunt Danger Beasts.
Number Three: Like me, he must have been
raised in the frontier rather than the capital.
"Number Four: I want someone
younger so I can dominate him."
"Number Five: He must be someone
with a pure and innocent smile."
The majority of people won't
even get past condition number one!
Yes, there aren't many men with
the potential to become generals.
What do you think of the contenders, General?
They're nothing but pathetic rabble
floundering through a street fight.
I seriously doubt we'll find
anyone who can wield an Imperial Arms.
Oh, it looks like these two are finished.
And the victory goes to Nobunaga!
That's how it goes!
This next bout is going to be the final match.
To my left:
Kalbi the Butcher!
To my right:
Tatsumi the Blacksmith!
He picked an interesting fake job.
Think he knows anything about blacksmithing?
Well, he's not as good as me,
but I guess he's decent with his hands.
I see one of them is pretty young.
Well, look at you, little fella!
Looks like that prize money is as good as mine!
I trained at Imperial Fist Temple.
I was second degree when they kicked me out!
The big fella's not all talk. He looks pretty strong.
He might've intimidated me a few months ago,
but I'm a lot different now.
Compared to those Three Beasts I
fought before, this guy is nothing!
You may begin!
You will feel the full force of my Explosive Iron Fists!
I can beat this guy without Incursio!
Yah!
Hyah!
Yaaahhh!
Yah!
He might be small, but he's rather talented.
Yes...
And there you have it!
Tatsumi wins!
Are all these people cheering for me?
This is awesome!
He's the one.
He's our Imperial Arms candidate?
Oh, yes, that. But that's not all.
Commander?
She's coming into the ring herself?!
Tatsumi? Is that right? That's a lovely name.
Um, thank you.
So this is Esdeath.
The one everyone's talking about.
If it weren't for her, we wouldn't have lost Bro.
You put on an impressive show.
Now, for your reward...
Oh, uh, thank you very much, ma'am.
No matter how you get it, money is still money.
And I have no problem taking it.
Huh?
Starting today, you'll be mine and mine alone.
Uh, wait a sec-.
Let's go somewhere we can be alone.
Too many eyes around here.
Stop it!
Be a good boy. Okay?
What'd... she do to me?
We'll talk further in my room,
just the two of us.
What the hell just happened?!
So Esdeath took Tatsumi away with her?!
Has she figured out he's a member of Night Raid yet?
I can't really say for sure. It's probably a 50/50 chance.
The last thing we saw was her
trying to drag him into the palace.
What should we do now, Akame?
Tatsumi...
I won't ever make you sad again, Akame.
Please don't say something
stupid like we need to save him.
That won't work.
The first thing we should do is
move our base further from town.
Good thinking. We're too easy to spot here.
Okay, but what about Tatsumi?
I'm not trying to say you would, but...
No, I understand.
I won't go charging in without a plan.
But Tatsumi is still a member of our team!
Do whatever it takes!