But why? Why would you allow them to die just to save me?
Get over yourself.
If we hadn't stopped that execution it would've
seriously damaged the Revolutionary Army's morale.
Besides, everyone participated of their own free will.
Yeah, well that's not the point.
Furthermore... we managed to eliminate a
long-standing obstacle when we killed Great General Budo.
We've gained a lot from this mission.
Is that all that matters to you?!
Tatsumi, you do realize this whole
thing's been hard on the Boss too, right?
She lost Susanoo.
These things happen.
It was doing its job as a weapon, that's all.
Poor Su.
As the living it is our responsibility
to carry out the wishes of the ones who are gone.
I don't know if I can.
It may be heavy, but it's a burden
that none of us have the right to abandon.
Akame...
In other words, if we quit now...
then all the dead will have died for nothing!
Yeah, you're right!
I guess somebody has to put an end to all this sadness.
In order to use his trump card,
Susanoo needed to take my life.
But I'm still here...
Susanoo, did you burn through your
own life energy to keep from killing me?
You were never just an Imperial Arms.
You were an irreplaceable... companion.
Do you... remember what you told me?
You said that you were gonna make something
of your life and rid this world of intolerance.
I'll do it, Mine.
I'll make your wish come true.
I promise.
Lemme go!
Keep up this rebellious crap
and I'll put you under arrest!
This place is a joke; Can't you
see it's falling apart around us!
What was that?!
No! Don't!
Hm...
Hmph!
How much longer do we have to put up with this?!
It'll be over soon.
The Empire's on its way down.
Most of the people we were supposed to
protect are now siding with the Revolution.
Is there still a place for us here anymore?
Try to stay calm.
The chaos probably won't stop even after the revolution.
And when the time comes, the
people are going to need our help.
It kinda sounds like you knew this would happen.
Well, it came a little earlier than I thought it would.
Huh?
I was desperately hoping for reform.
That's why I joined the Jaegers, to try to
make a difference in this nation from the inside.
To make a difference?
This Empire has become corrupt.
That said, I think this kind of rebellion is unacceptable.
So you chose to work under General Esdeath.
Yes.
I actually find her quite fascinating.
You are a strange guy y'know that.
Hm... I get that a lot.
Y'know my initial intention for joining was
to rise up in the ranks, but I got sidetracked.
Because I've enjoyed my time with everyone here so much.
Speaking of which, Kurome, what are you planning on doing?
Since you've got one foot in the grave.
Huh? Wait a minute, how did you find out about Kurome?!
You shouldn't be all that surprised, Wave.
It's obvious by the way you've been acting.
Ah!
At this point, you could probably be free from
the Jaegers without becoming a target, yourself.
Be free?
Yes.
I don't have any need for a brief taste of freedom.
There's only one thing I care about in this world.
Now this is the kind of battle I enjoy the most!
If any of you neophytes are unsatisfied with
your destiny, I invite you to put me in my place!
You can go to Hell!
As soon as you're dead this corrupt nation is finished!
Oh, an Imperial Arms?
How cute.
Is there not a single one of you who can challenge me?
Tatsumi escaped certain death against unbelievable odds.
We're simply meant to be together.
Wait for me, my love.
I'm coming for you.
Once I've cleaned up this mess.
The Imperial Capital is almost completely surrounded now!
What the hell is going on out there?!
Not even General Esdeath is capable of leading
an army in every direction at the same time!
Your Highness!
The Empire is crumbling under our reign...
have we not been good rulers?
There's nothing wrong with your rule, Your Majesty.
Oh, Minister Honest!
You idiots should be more supportive.
They've let their fear get the best of them.
I hate to say it, but I am painfully
aware of your feelings on this matter.
These men are fools!
They don't understand all the strides
you've taken to keep our land peaceful.
The citizens have started to rebel against us.
Please tell me what we should do!
There comes a time when a nation's ruler is
called to show his leadership with an iron fist.
You must make your authority known to your people!
Show your strength!
Huh? It couldn't be...
Now they'll see the Emperor's power...
I don't... have much time.
So... let's finish this... Big Sister.
Revolutionary spies.
I take it this is a warning.
I cannot believe what I'm seeing.
Huh?! It's a message for me.
Huh? It's a message?
I'm being challenged to a duel.
Uh? What does it say?
"Come to the Kadai Forest Institution ruins."
This is stupid! You know it's a trap!
If it was a trap they wouldn't
have waited this long to come for me.
It's a personal grudge.
A grudge? Then who is it?
Kurome's ready to settle things between us.
Uh!
Does it have to be right now?
Is this fight really all that important to you two?
Mm-hm.
Akame I'm sure you know that the lives of
thousands of people are resting on our shoulders!
How can you put this personal
vendetta over everything else?
That's exactly why I have to do this.
No matter what, I can't ignore Kurome's feelings.
She's the enemy.
She's my sister. Hm.
I'm the only person she knows who can truly understand...
what she's going through.
If you say so.
But I'm coming too.
You can't.
The revolution is going to need every
bit of your strength for the final siege.
Do not forget what your mission is.
Okay fine, but promise me you'll come back alive.
Tatsumi, please.
That's what you're always telling me to do.
So I expect the same thing from you.
Fine... you have my word.
I knew you'd show up...
Akame.
Hello Kurome.
You wanna snack?
Hm.
You remember this place, don't you?
This isn't the first time we've met here.
It's also the place...
where you turned your back on us.
Seems like the perfect place for me to kill you.
It sure takes me back.
No matter what happened to us, you were
always right there looking out for me.
We didn't have anyone but each other,
and this was the only place we felt needed.
They trained us to be assassins for the Empire.
We learned to stop uprisings before they started.
That was the way we were taught to protect the peace.
Under orders, we learned to kill
anyone who might be a threat to the Empire.
As far as we knew, we were doing the right thing.
Big Sister! Haha!
Kurome.
I missed you.
After being raised in two different squads,
we finally got the chance to be together again.
You came as a replacement for someone who'd been killed.
After that, the two of us were inseparable...
like we were trying to make up
for all the time we'd been apart.
We were the ultimate team.
Some of our missions were difficult,
but I made it through because I had you.
If you were with me, I was happy.
But... then...
But then you betrayed the Empire and joined Night Raid.
Why?! I tried so hard to stop you!
Being abandoned by my own sister absolutely crushed me.
Every day since you left, I've been
imagining more and more ways to kill you.
Is killing me gonna solve your problems?
There is no solution.
However, if I kill you...
then you can be beside me for all eternity.
Using an Imperial Arms is very strenuous.
It must be unbearable when you're so weak.
I can end your suffering.
Haha! Sister, it's time for us to fight... to the death.
Kurome.
I guess she's gone.
She needed to take care of some unfinished business.
Why would she leave without saying anything about it?
If she'd said something, you would have tried to stop her.
Do you have any idea where she could've gone?
Maybe a place that's important to the two of them?
Why did you have to leave and betray the squad?
Everything would have been fine
between us if you hadn't run away!
I learned a lot about life from going on my own.
And I realized that we were never
fighting for the good of the nation!
We were only doing the Empire's dirty work!
Murdering people without question!
The way things stand, no good is
ever going to come from this government.
It's why I wanted you to leave with me.
How could you expect me to do that when so many
others were forced to die for the sake of their missions?!
All that sadness was caused by the leaders of the Empire!
If we can bring happiness to people by overthrowing
the leadership, I know our comrades would understand!
That's a selfish excuse!
Huh?
Danger Beast.
It must've come out of hiding
when it sensed our desire to fight!
Kurome!
Ah!
Natara!
You will pay for hurting my friends!
Doya!
No!
Alright that's it!
I don't have any more time to waste on you!
That was really close. Are you okay?
Akame.
Let's go get him.
Hm.
You're done!
Looks like you and I still have what it takes.
The two of us always were pretty good at this weren't we?
You remember don't you, Big Sister?!
Haha...
Get her!
I should've known my pawns couldn't handle it.
This battle... IS OVER!
I won't let you hurt Kurome!
Wave?!
C'mon, Night Raid, I'm your target now!
What the?!
Move, Tatsumi!
You move, Wave!
Huh?
But you're my teammate; I can't just walk away from you!
But I want you to.
Kurome...
What are you doing here, Tatsumi?!
I came to make sure no one interferes with your fight.
Huh?
Hm.
Tatsumi, we don't have time for this!
I wish I could stop them too!
But if I did that, then they'd never
be able to finally sort this thing out!
Is this how Night Raid assassins
settle their differences?!
I cannot allow it to happen!
This a matter of the heart!
Sometimes there are problems that can only
be solved by yourself... without any help!
A matter of the heart?
I...
Wave.
Thank you for coming to help me.
Maybe if things had gone differently... The
two of us could've been friends or something.
But Kurome...
It's time for us to finally deal with all
the regret and pain we've had for so long.
It's time to end this.
Are you ready? Let's go.
Kurome... my little sister.
Mmhmm.
You know I've always loved you, Big Sister.
This couldn't be the only way for
them to resolve their differences.
I wasn't able to help her...
I couldn't do anything to stop it!
You came to look after my little sister.
That's enough.
No... no...
Damn it!
I don't understand.
I don't know why...
why we're even fighting each other anymore.
If you can't find a reason to
fight then you shouldn't be fighting.
Only those who fully comprehend the
implications of war can be capable of bearing arms.
Implications?
You'll bear this weight for the rest of your life.
Akame!
Didn't I tell you to stay back?
Yeah, maybe during the fight.
But you never said anything about coming to
take care of an injured companion, now did you?
Huh?
I've said goodbye to so many of my friends along the way.
But that's nothing...
compared to all the loss you've
been through your whole life.
I couldn't even begin to comprehend your pain.
Huh!
Akame...
you're not gonna lose any more loved ones.
Ever again.
I'm so pleased you came to this decision!
What a wise ruler you are!
Now, open your Imperial Arms passed
down through generations of royalty!
Those insufferable revolutionaries...
as well as the brainless masses...
soon they'll know your supremacy!
This is our Empire.
We must use our powers to defend this land.