General Esdeath...
For your success in conquering the northern tribe,
we have arranged a reward of 10,000 gold coins.
I'm grateful, Your Highness.
I'll send it to the soldiers
still fighting to protect our land.
They will be pleased.
Esdeath truly doesn't care for money or power.
She is only concerned with war and victory.
As long as I'm in control, she
can destroy whatever she wishes.
Our interests can coexist.
She is the ideal puppet.
Now that I've returned to the capital from the
northlands, Your Majesty can once again rest at ease.
I shall be terminating Night Raid next.
Quite an undertaking.
We would like to compensate you for such an
ambitious achievement with more than just money.
Is there something else you'd prefer?
Actually, there is. If I could choose anything...
Go on.
I believe I'd like to try falling in love.
Uh, yes, that sounds reasonable!
You are a single woman of marriageable age, after all!
I will serve as your matchmaker!
So what is your opinion of the minister here?
Huh? Wait, what?!
The Minister doesn't take very good care of himself.
He will not live much longer.
Preposterous! I'm in perfect health.
Well then, would you be so kind
as to tell us what you'd like?
First, let me warn you that I can be terribly selective.
Very few men will come close to my expectations.
Once I'm ready, I will present you with
an extensive list of my preferences.
Here.
I don't need you to spoon-feed me!
But it'll get cold.
Okay, I guess you win.
Even after what happened...
Akame's so calm.
I still can't believe it.
I can't believe that girl killed Sheele.
I'm finally starting to realize...
how painful this job really is.
You know, it's strange.
I don't normally take an interest
in anything besides war and bloodshed.
Oh, we're talking about love, I presume?
I don't even understand this myself, but
I'm feeling a desperate need for romance.
Desire for the opposite sex is
something all living creatures feel.
I don't know if I'd use the word "romance" in your case.
It's interesting, yet it's still an animalistic instinct.
But for the moment, I must channel all
my energy into eliminating Night Raid.
Ah, while we're on the subject.
I've come up with a new idea that I think you'll like.
I have a special assignment
for you, my precious Three Beasts.
We will do anything you command us to do, General Esdeath.
Yes ma'am, all of us are your
loyal and devoted servants forever!
No matter what you wish, we will
carry out any order at any time.
Good.
Man, it's cold.
How am I supposed to sleep like this?
I'll get some water.
Akame?
Late-night snack?
No, but they were always one of Sheele's favorites.
It's an offering.
Since our work's always been done behind the scenes,
Sheele's name probably isn't in
the Revolutionary record books.
So if I don't hold on to her memory,
then it'll be just like she was never here.
She might have been absentminded,
but she was the kindest person on the team.
I agree.
And I see you still leave flowers at Sayo
and Ieyasu's graves sometimes too, don't you?
Yeah.
Akame, you're pretty amazing.
You're handling your friend's death so calmly.
I guess you're used to it.
I still can't-.
You think that I'm...
I'm used to it?
Akame?
Sure... maybe I've witnessed
more deaths than I care to count.
But this... you don't ever get used to it!
Godammit! You just hide it and you finish the mission!
I have to act like everything is okay,
but on the inside, I've been falling apart!
We're assassins, Tatsumi,
we have to be able to switch things on and off.
You... You think that I'm calm?
Well you're wrong! You don't know what it's
like! You don't know what losing her means to me!
You don't know...
I've never seen Akame break down like this.
I guess I shouldn't be surprised.
She was pretty worried about me on my first mission.
What the hell's wrong with me?
Feeling sorry for myself isn't gonna bring Sheele back!
I just need to move on and remember why I'm here!
I need to grow up and just be a man!
It's a dirty job, but money is money,
and I have to keep my village from
starving until the revolution is over.
I have to do what I can for the people I care about most!
What did you do that for?! Tatsumi, are you all right?
Yeah, I just needed to get my head
back together. Don't worry about me.
I also wanna tell you that I'm sorry.
That was insensitive of me.
And I wanna renew my pledge to you:
I promise you I won't die and I
won't ever make you sad again, Akame!
Tatsumi...
We're gonna make it through to the end.
I want to see the new nation together!
Yeah. I'd like that.
YAH!
Crap!
One more round, all right?
Don't you think you might need
to rest up a little bit first?
I don't have time for that!
Remember, we're pretending this
is a real fight, so don't hold back!
Here I coooome...
Dammit, Bro, what was that for?!
If you want to pretend it's for real, you
should pay more attention to what's around you.
There could always be another enemy nearby. Understand?
Well, somebody seems a little on edge today.
What's up?
Not much.
I just want to level up as fast as I can.
I have to keep my promise to Akame!
No matter what happens, I have to survive!
I hope so...
Now that's the kind of attitude I like to see!
You've come pretty far! Say!
Why don't you try sparring with me for a little while?
I can whip you into shape!
Sure! Great!
You watch yourself! I'm pretty good with a spear!
Heads up!
Is that really all you got?!
Takes more than passion to stay alive, you know!
Yeah! Yaaahhh!
Now come at me!
Good luck.
Yet another devastated village.
A nation is nothing without its people.
You really do care, don't you, Father?
Enough to return to the snake pit of the capital.
It makes me proud.
This is no time to cower in
retirement and let life pass me by.
I intend to fight that minister till my very last breath.
And I intend to watch over you every step of the way!
I'm lucky to have such a brave daughter.
Now, if only you wouldn't scare away all of your suitors.
Wha-?! Now what does that have to do with anything?!
What's happening out there?!
More bandits...
This area's getting worse all the time!
Don't worry, Father. I'll take care of this!
Everyone, ready!
Daidara...
Yep!
Take 'em out!
YAH-HA!
I'm sorry, Father...
Well, you're a feisty one, aren't cha?
But considering everything I'm about to do to you,
you're probably gonna wish you'd been killed already.
You... you're an Imperial officer!
I am, and I once had a deep
respect for your diplomacy, sir.
Then why in God's name would you do something like this?!
Because my master ordered it.
And the wishes of my master shall always be realized.
Look at this. We took out like 15 guys.
Sweet, man! I'm gonna get so
many experience points for this!
Don't forget the notices.
If you ask me, the minister's idea's a pain in the ass.
Why not pin it on his political
enemies like he usually does?
Because this plan would have no effect on
officials under the protection of Great General Budo.
Ah, are we done already?
Nyau, stop screwing around!
You did make sure to finish her off, didn't you?
I was just in the middle of skinning her face
when she died of shock.
You are one messed-up kid, you know that?
The mission is now complete. Let's be on our way.
Now that everyone is here,
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
Esdeath has taken the northern tribe, and
has now returned to the Imperial Capital.
Leone I would like you to make your way to the
capital and figure out what General Esdeath is up to.
You got it! I've been wondering what that chick is like!
She's a disturbed psychopath obsessed with killing.
Don't be careless.
All right, don't worry.
That means I can waste her if
I get the chance, doesn't it?
I heard that wackjob is the
strongest person in the empire.
That puts her right up there
with the minister on our hit list!
Also, ever since her arrival in the capital,
there's been an increase in
assassinations of imperial officials.
As of today, four officers and
61 bodyguards have been murdered.
What concerns me are these flyers
they've been scattering around
that claim Night Raid is responsible for the homicides.
So they're trying to stick the whole thing on us, huh?
But doesn't this sorta stuff always get straightened out?
Those posters really don't look all that legit.
That's how most people felt about it at first.
But now, public opinion is starting to change.
But why?!
All of the victims had first-rate
guards when the crimes were committed.
They couldn't have been overpowered by ordinary thugs.
So basically, these guys are
going after the big fish on purpose.
Only a few people could pull that off.
That would only be us or someone equally skilled.
It's safe to assume two things:
They probably have Imperial Arms,
and they're working for General Esdeath.
What is she trying to accomplish?
She's trying to trick us.
She wants to lure us out in the open so she can strike.
Now that we know it's a trap, I
want to throw one more thing out there.
The people they're assassinating
are all competent individuals
who disagree with the minister's policies
and recognize the need for revolution.
After we create the new nation,
allies like them will be crucial to its success.
To put it simply:
We cannot afford to continue losing them.
I'd like to hear everyone's thoughts.
Listen...
I don't know very much about all this political stuff,
but the idea of somebody abusing Night
Raid's name like that really pisses me off!
Tatsumi...
You know, you're exactly right.
Thanks, man.
Good! That settles it.
Show the bastards what happens when they use our name.
Night Raid will not be sullied.
There are two of us that they'll likely target next:
Akame and Lubbock.
Tatsumi and Bulat, you will
guard the person I assign to you.
Sounds good to me. Just tell us where to
meet him, and we'll take care of everything.
Your charge will be boarding a cruise ship currently
docked at the grand canal near the Imperial Capital...
the Ryusen!
It's... It's huge!!
Looks more like a fortress than a cruise ship.
Should be an interesting place to intercept our targets.
Rice reserves, huh? Must be pretty smart.
All that rice will make a lot of people happy.
I guess I made myself hungry just looking at it.
You can have my rations if you take out
any enemies that pop up. We got a deal?
No action here.
Looks like we completely missed the mark this time.
Don't let your guard down yet.
I know, I won't.
Tatsumi... Bulat...
If they're going after your target...
Please... come back safe!
The guy we're protecting is surrounded by bodyguards.
There's no way anyone could even get close to 'em.
They probably aren't gonna show up.
The hell was that?
Don't be so quick to assume, Tatsumi.
Wait... Bro?!
My trump card is invisibility, remember?
And you never know what our foes might do.
Yeah, you're right.
I guess I didn't think that through, did I?
How many times would you say you've
smacked me in the head, by the way?
Eh, sometimes you need a little tough love.
Love... love...
Did you really have to make it echo?!
Well anyway, I bet this armor
is really cool to have around.
It certainly made it easy to sneak up onto the ship.
That's right. Got me through
the battle with the southern tribe.
I kinda like to think of it as my partner.
However, when it comes to partnerships,
sometimes things aren't always so simple.
Sir! I don't understand!
I mean how can they just discharge you from the capital?!
I couldn't stand the thought of having
to bribe the new minister, so I refused.
So if you want to move up in rank,
you just have to give him some money?!
That's bullshit!
Calm yourself, Bulat.
I am going back to the capital to plead my case.
Despite the position I'm in at the
moment, I have done nothing wrong.
I am confident that the court will see that.
General...
It wasn't fair that you were
placed under an officer like me.
I hope you can forgive me.
Of course... I admire you.
But as you can imagine, the court
didn't end up ruling in his favor.
And then some people who were jealous of
my ability started saying I was a criminal.
I was getting sick of it.
So I used Incursio to escape before they could catch me.
Man, that's so messed up.
Looks like my invisibility's wearing off.
Better remove my armor.
But they know your face from all the posters.
You can let me handle the open public areas, okay?
Good thinking! I'll go check the ship's hold.
I'd better keep an eye out for
anybody who looks suspicious.
Ha! Though I guess I look pretty suspicious myself.
Who's playing a flute?
I'll have your best dessert.
Uh yes, comin' right up.
She's sitting right out in the open.
I can sense it.
This is a trap to draw us out!
That evil woman!
She's oozing with the scent of hatred!
I can smell it all over her!
It was stupid of me to think I could take
her out just because she was easy to find!
It kills me, but I must follow my instincts and withdraw.
The aura's gone.
I guess they didn't take the bait.
And I'd hoped to test out some new torture techniques.
My, that's pretty good.
Perhaps I'll treat everyone when this job is done.
Your sweet melody sounds as elegant as ever.
The cruise ship has left the Imperial Capital
and no one can see us from the shore.
It appears the timing will be perfect.
I've been playing for a long time now, so
all the passengers should be nice and drowsy!
There may be people on board who don't
appreciate the beauty of your music.
You'll have to be wary.
Of course...
What the heck is going on?
That flute must be causing this.
I gotta get outside!
I can still hear it out here!
It has to be an Imperial Arms.
Hey little fella, it's supposed to be nap time.
And here I was gonna let you live if you were sleepin'.
You must be one of those Night
Raid posers I've heard about.
Does that mean you think you're the real deal?
This should be good.
Heads up!
Hey, what's the sword for?
Gotta fight fair.
I wanna make sure I get experience points for this.
Always looking to get stronger.
Come at me, little man!
Uh, fine.
I'll give you some experience.
But it's not gonna be pretty!
Ah, nice! I like that confidence!
Man, it's gonna be fun to crush you!
Heh, heh!
Amazing you could dodge that after the music debuff.
That's okay.
Let's see how you handle this!
Are those things your Imperial Arms?
Yup! Double Great Axes Belvaac.
Bet a low-level punk like you can't even hit it!
In that case...
I guess I'll just have to make it hit you!
Tatsumi, you idiot!
That guy was obviously getting
ready to finish you off and you just
barreled right in there without even thinking about it!
You need to learn to be more responsible!
Hang on! How do you have so much energy?
The Song of Lethargy was supposed
to put everybody on the boat to sleep.
So that's what all that racket was about?
Cheap crap like that doesn't work on me.
What?
If you think playing a little tune is enough
to smother the burning passion in my soul,
then you've got another thing coming, my friend!
Wait a sec...
Okay, I see what you did there.
You stabbed yourself so you'd be
too distracted to hear the lullaby.
The name's Bulat of Night Raid.
You can also call me "Handsome".
Yeah, I don't think so, jackass.
I'm Daidara, servant of Esdeath.
Tatsumi...
It's very important for you to pay
close attention to how I fight, okay?
Bro?
Incursio!
I am gonna get a ton of experience points for this guy!
Behind you!
He's mine! I'm gonna crack his skull open!
See?
This is what I meant when I told you
to always be aware of your surroundings.
He slaughtered the big guy AND
got the other two off his back.
And... he did it in a split second!
Whoa, I always knew you were a good fighter,
but that was awesome!
Damn straight! Back in my soldier days,
they used to call me Hundred-Man Slayer.
I believe it was a 128, to be exact.
You played a vital role in getting rid of
covert operatives back then, did you not?
I'd know that power and that armor anywhere.
It truly has been a while, hasn't it, Bulat?
It's you...
General Liver!