Another castle surrendered without a fight!
Cowards. Don't these people have any loyalty anymore?
The viceroys of these castles
were relocated to the countryside
because their behavior showed signs
of insubordination against His Majesty.
It comes as no surprise.
But Minister, if this continues, the
rebel army will reach the Imperial...
There's no need to panic.
Great General Budo!
A general should refrain from
getting involved in politics.
I've lived by those words for quite some time now.
However I'm finding it a challenge to keep my mouth
shut when it comes to something like this, Minister.
Hohoho... I'm not sure what to say!
I will protect this Empire.
It is a responsibility handed down through
my family line for the past thousand years.
As such, I will personally annihilate anyone who
dares to disrupt the peace of this great nation...
regardless of who may interfere.
Admirable! But there's no reason for concern.
Even if the citizens rise in rebellion,
we have plans in place to overpower them.
Gentlemen...
Allow me to introduce an elite force
I've assembled to protect the Capital.
Hello Hellooo.
This is my son, Syura.
I've decided to appoint him to
serve as the company's commander.
Hm? You must be the "Great"
General I've heard so much about.
You're like tied with Esdeath for scariest in the Empire.
Anyway, you shouldn't waste time worrying
about some commoners and their revolution bullshit.
Why not let me handle it?
Oh? Going out?
If there's one thing I've learned from battle,
it's that you can always find a few rats around
before the entire swarm makes an appearance.
Seriously.
Can't he just sit in the castle and look pretty.
Listen, Son.
This is your chance to prove yourself.
Whether or not I choose you to be my
successor will depend on your performance.
Very well. Hope you enjoy the show.
But first, I have a few rats
of my own to hunt down. Hehe...
It's so empty in here lately.
Kurome, do you feel better now? Honestly?
I'm... okay.
Hmm...
I did the best I could,
but I doubt it'll taste as good as what Bols used to make.
Wave, have you heard about the new security force?
Apparently they report directly to the Minister.
Yeah?
Well, I suppose we probably should've seen it coming.
The Commander's on an expedition, and
half our team members have been assassinated.
But isn't that even more of a reason to
move the rest of the Jaegers to the frontline?
Why would they put us on standby?
It tells me that there must be some
disagreement in the Capital's central command.
What the hell are they thinking?!
It's times like these we have to pull together.
It's the only way to bring down the Revolutionary Army.
More please!
Are you serious?
Jeez. How can you even eat at a time like this?
Help yourself.
Uh...
She fainted!
Oh God!
Kurome!
What's wrong?!
Can you hear me?
Kurome!
Wake up!
Open your eyes!
Kurome!
They're sending out more soldiers.
Yeah. This place is starting to look like a battlefield.
So the plan is to wait out here for the
perfect moment and sneak into the palace.
And then we can kill the Minister.
Are you sure you're ready to do this, Tatsumi?
It's what we have to do.
Remember, it's important that we minimize
the number of innocent people involved.
The best way to do that is get rid
of the Minister as quickly as possible.
Well put.
Oh, it's almost time for our meeting with the resistance.
Let's go.
It's hard to believe how complex these waterways are.
I think they got bigger as the
Imperial Capital got bigger...
pretty wild.
But their maintenance is crap, and
it's impossible to find a good map.
Well on the bright side, I bet there's
a way we can use it to our advantage.
So... Mine.
Hmm? Uh-oh, why the sudden change in tone?
Hehehe!
So like what is the story on you and Tatsumi?
Ah! Whaaat?!
Oh come on, you don't think I wasn't gonna notice.
I mean seriously, you two've been all
cute and awkward since we left Kyoroku.
Hey now you wait just a minute!
There's nothing going on between me and that idiot,
are you looking for a punch in the face or something?!
Aww, it's okay, you don't have
to get all flustered about it!
What?! Whatever, I'm not getting all flustered!
Well, if that's how you're gonna be about
it... Then I guess he's up for grabs then!
Uh?
Oh hell no!
You are really pathetic.
That's adorable, but I'm still taking Tatsumi for myself!
Hmph!
Quit screwing around and get back to work! Let's go!
Not flustered at all.
Got it.
Continue the mission as planned.
Right! You can count on us.
Apparently we're no longer in
contact with the western tribe.
Hm? Really?
It's fine. I was expecting this.
Let's not deviate from the plan.
When we storm the palace...
I would like the two of you to take the lead.
Don't fail me!
Understood.
Tatsumi, Lubbock.
Please get through this.
Hey, Tatsumi.
Hm?
What are you gonna do when the revolution's over?
Uh... hmm... I dunno...
I guess I never really thought about it.
What about you? You got plans?
Well, I've been running that bookstore on the side.
I'll probably just stick with that.
Maybe I could make it a national chain or something.
Wow.
And then!
When the timing's right I'll ask Najenda to marry me!
Oh, is that so? That sounds nice.
While we're on the subject,
what's going on with you and Mine?
Huh?! What does she have to do with this?!
Aw, don't be shy!
Everybody can tell there's been a little spark
between the two of you love birds
ever since we got back from Kyoroku.
So spill it!
Tell me how far have you gotten with her.
Ooh, you've at least landed a smooch, right?
Cut it out!
Uh, pardon me...
Huh?
You're uh...
members of Night Raid, right?
Uh...
Ah!
Lemme guess you must be with the resistance.
I am.
Once we go inside, we'll have to be very quiet.
Okay.
I gotta say I'm surprised a high-class
lady like you would be part of the resistance.
My father was one of the Emperor's instructors,
but the Minister accused him of having
ulterior motives against the Empire.
He threw my father and my mother in prison.
Well now I get it.
So that means...
even more people in the palace
must support the revolution.
Yes.
They've united under a group of anti-Minister bureaucrats,
who stay in close contact with the Revolutionary Army.
And it's up to us to help those guys get the
revolutionaries gathered together from the inside,
once the siege on the palace actually goes down.
Alright. Perfect.
Good to know we're not alone.
We were chosen over everyone else for this
job because of my stealth and your invisibility.
We can't screw up!
Hm. Hm.
This is it.
Huh?
You alright?
Something's wrong.
Whenever I knock twice, someone's supposed
to respond back with a password knock.
Uh!
Stand back.
Hm?
Huh?
Whoa.. What happened here?!
This isn't good guys; They already found the hideout.
Huh?!
Get out, NOW!
Uuh...
Huh?
Hm!
Hehe...
Took you long enough; I've been waiting forever.
Hate to be the one to break it to you, but I had
to eliminate all those idiots with the "resistance".
You may call me the Great Syura!
You two are with the Night Raid, yes?
You had better be worth all the trouble.
Huh?
Oh! You must be the little shit with General Esdeath
when I sent her to that deserted island or whatever?
So I guess you must've been
responsible for the Danger Beasts!
Why'd you do it?
Why do anything?
'Cause it's amusing, young man!
There's nothing in this world that
bothers me more than being bored.
And those creatures kept me pretty well entertained.
That's enough... eat this!
Tatsumi!
Wh... what the?!
Just as I thought, a few rats have found their way in.
Uh...
Oh! I'm always up for a visit from my Uncle Budo.
I'll let you take care of the pipsqueak.
Exactly what I had in mind.
I am known as Budo.
His Majesty the Emperor granted
me the title of Great General.
I've heard rumors about this monster.
You are villainous trash threatening
the Empire... you are finished.
Now face your judgment.
And feel the Wrath of the Lightning God Adramelech!
Tatsumi!
Uh... How did he manage to do that?
He never even touched me!
Impressive.
Not many men can dodge my attack.
I see determination in your eyes.
Errr..
Incursio!
Be careful with that guy!
Hehehe...
Huh?
What?! How'd you do that?!
I think you're gonna be a fun one to mess with.
Leave him to me, guys!
This precious little victim is all mine.
Err...
I quite enjoyed that.
As one might expect, the atmosphere of the
battlefield suits me far better than bodyguard duty.
It's time to return to the Capital.
It won't be long, Night Raid.
What?!
Don't forget to look behind you, Night Raid!
Well now!
What do we have here?
A seamstress?
Ooh, don't get such a pouty face;
I'm about to share with you a secret.
I call this little toy "Shambhala."
It gives me the ability to teleport
either myself or my adversaries...
Huh?!
To anywhere I've left my pretty little mark!
He can manipulate space!
But the damn thing does wear me out. I couldn't
use it in quick succession until just recently.
Then I found this juicy-stuff when I got to the Capital.
It really lets me "cut loose", if you will!
As you can see... I got a little carried
away and put markers all over the place!
What's wrong?
Not gonna run?
Aww, man!
You giving up already? Hehe...
Getting away from him won't do any good!
No matter where I run, he can warp right up to me!
But...
He can't follow me somewhere he hasn't marked!
Ha!
Aaah... Urg!
Did that get you all pissy?
So I guess you can put up markers in midair can't ya.
Bingo, smarty pants.
Think I'd leave you a safe place to hide?
You've nowhere to run!
He hits hard but his movements are exaggerated.
I can take him!
Ah!
Young man, I'm curious what is your name?
Huh...
Tell me who you are.
Or perhaps assassins like you don't have names?
It's Tatsumi!
Tatsumi.
Seems to be a sincere boy; And honest enough.
And not a hint of hesitation in his posture.
I can only imagine the amount of training
it took for him to achieve this level of skill.
Even so...
Uh!
I am charged with the termination of any
who mean to bring harm to his Imperial Majesty!
Tatsumi!
Uh... Huh?
Hey, what're you doing?
I'm sorry! I have to do this...
I have to, for my mother...
Stop it, let me go!
I'm sorry...
Didn't I tell you to stay out of this?
Huh... Stupid toys should not
be interfering with my plans.
She's a... a toy?
Uh-huh. Everything from these morons
to the Capital itself, are my toys!
Pretty soon I'll leave my old man in the
dust, and they'll be crowning me emperor!
Hey now, don't tell me you're quitting.
We're only just getting started, sonny!
No... it's over.
And it looks like you lose.
Huh?
Uh?
Owwwww!
Don't move!
Or I'll have to take off something bigger next time.
Damn you!
Huh? What's this?!
A barrier of World-Severing String.
I'd already used a lot, but I had
just enough left to pull this together.
Son of a bitch! You set this up while you were running!
You gave me plenty of time.
And all of your bragging and showing off gave me a
pretty good indication of where all the markers were.
You little shit!
Listen up! All of you, drop your weapons now!
Syura, I've got a few questions that I need to ask you.
Guh!
Uh... You...
Please, Lord Syura...
I did as I was ordered...
now please, release my family...
Hehehe...
No can do, sweetie!
Haha... Sorry to tell you, but
Mommy and Daddy died a long time ago!
Hahaha...
Okay, Night Raid, I've really had a marvelous time. But...
It's time we wrapped this up.
I'd like to express my gratitude
by letting you see my trump card.
Bon voyage!
You're off to the ends of the Earth!
No one's ever made it back from out there!
You're gonna die alone in the
emptiness of space, Night Raid!
Hahahaha...
Huh?
No!
That son of a bitch!
Nothing in this world or the next could
possibly break the World-Severing String!
Not even an Imperial Arms that controls space!
So, here we go again.
God dammit... Ah!
You cannot get away!
It's only right that we finish this fairly.
If I'm going to die, then you're going down with me.
The hell I am!
I won't allow myself to die with rabble like you!
I haven't had time to take this boring bland
vanilla nation and give it the fun it deserves!
Kind of a crazy sentiment...
but believe it or not, I do think I understand.
No, I'm not supposed to die yet!
I have so much to do!
So you wanna change the world? Huh?
Course you do.
Everybody wants to do that, asshole.
But still...
none of that gives you the right to treat your fellow
human beings like they're your own personal playthings
and to treat them like they're nothing!
Uh...
Thanks for protecting me so long, Cross Tail.
I'm sorry, Najenda.
This was as far as I could go.
I'm leaving the rest to you, Tatsumi.
Uh...
Oh, Lubb...
Aaaugh!
He's dead!
How could you leave me?!
Oh well!
Can't change anything by grieving over the fallen, can we?
Well he did manage to eliminate a Night Raid assassin.
Rather fair trade if you ask me.
I took the liberty of confining the
other Night Raid member to the dungeon.
Excellent work.
Let's see... now...
If we wish to subdue the rebels,
I imagine we need to make an example of that boy.
It must be bold.
So I wonder what's the best
form of torture to make a point.
Hmm... You're still as depraved
as ever, aren't you, Minister?
Listen. Punishing a rebel calls
for a higher grade of cruelty.
I have a few suggestions...
Hm?
I couldn't help but overhear your conversation.
And if I may, I'd like that job to be mine.
Ohh?
Tatsumi, I won't let anyone take you from me!
An execution? Oh no...
Uh! Oh God... no...