I'm going.
And I won't let you stop me.
It's a trap.
I don't need you to tell me that.
But still... I won't just sit
here and watch them execute Tatsumi!
You've really changed, Mine.
Remember when you were trying to stop me?
Please don't say something stupid like
we need to save him. That won't work.
That was a long time ago.
Tatsumi means something different to me now.
I'm going too.
There's no reason to put
yourself in danger. That's stupid!
What you're planning is stupid!
If we do this together, we have a
greater chance of making it back.
Y'know, you're starting to sound just
like him with all that pathetic optimism.
You're just as bad as me, if not worse.
Fine, you can tag along if it means that much to you!
Sounds like a plan!
Leone!
I'm the one who saw Tatsumi's potential and
pushed for him to join us in the first place.
If he were to get himself executed at this point
in the game, it would make me look like a jerk.
So... Does that mean you're on board?
We've made up our minds, Boss.
Hope you're okay with it.
Why would I have a problem with that?
The boss?
If they're holding a public execution with the
intention of weakening the Revolutionary Army's morale,
then it's our responsibility to put a stop to it.
Besides, I have no doubt we're going to
need Tatsumi and Incursio in the final battle.
Awww! It's okay, we know you miss him.
Oh, you know I'm right.
Then consider this an emergency mission.
Let's go get Tatsumi.
Tatsumi...
It's been a while, Tatsumi.
I can't believe you were part of Night Raid.
I came in here ready to destroy you,
but all my anger was gone once I saw your face.
You must be so unhappy.
It's not too late to join me.
If you do, I promise I'll forgive all your transgressions.
Never! I will not fight for the Empire.
If you won't accept my offer,
then you know what must happen.
I will die for what I believe.
I won't ask where your friends are.
All I want is for you to stand beside me.
Why are you so fixated on me?
My heart was drawn to you.
I want us to be together, Tatsumi.
No!
I could never be with someone who's only desires
in this world are creating war and destruction!
Is that right?
Then have it your way.
I will perform your execution with my own hands.
That way I can see for myself
the strength of your resolve.
The commander said she was in love with Tatsumi, right?
So why is she doing this?
Well, I suppose you could
think of it as an act of passion.
Our orders were very clear.
Tomorrow during the execution, palace
defenses will be thinner than usual.
We'll be expected to provide backup.
But what is she thinking, killing the one she loves?
It just doesn't make sense to me.
I understand how she feels.
Instead of letting somebody else kill him,
she wants to be the one to do it.
Just like how I want to kill my sister.
It's because I love her.
But now... it's...
It's too late.
I'm out of time. I can't...
My sources have informed me that
the Great General Budo will be attending
the public execution along with Esdeath.
Who's Budo?
He's the only great general in the empire
and he has the loyalty of all the guards.
And his weapon, Adramelech, is quite terrifying.
Wow!
Susanoo?
Are you ready to use your trump card?
Yes, once you've given me the
word, I can activate it as needed.
We must complete this mission and
prove our comrades didn't die in vain.
Thank you for your loyal service.
Thank you, Lubbock.
People of this great nation!
We are most distraught by the rebels spreading
unfounded rumors about the fall of our empire.
Disregard these allegations.
We would like to assure you
that the empire is alive and well!
Today, one of their members shall be put to
death, in atonement for this traitorous behavior!
The Revolutionary Army has caused great unrest,
with these murderous criminals as their spearhead!
And by brandishing the blade of greed,
they've deceived honest people.
They're nothing but a violent gang of assassins!
No matter what your numbers,
and no matter what falsehoods you perpetuate,
We will not allow you to poison Our city!
Mark my words: Our great empire will never fall!
We've done well, haven't We, Minister?
Impeccable as always, Your Majesty.
General Esdeath, you may lop
off his head whenever you're ready.
Hold on. Where do you think you're going?
Excuse us, it's time for lunch.
Come along, Your Grace.
Lunch already?
Then, could you oversee the execution, Budo? Please?
Of course.
Oh, I'm quite famished!
So the minister's making his escape.
I know precisely where to cut whether
I want to maim or I want to kill.
You told me you were prepared to die, did you not?
If you're the man I think you are, then
you'll show me how strong your spirit is!
Way to go, dummy!
You weren't supposed to get caught, y'know!
Oh, no. What're you doing?!
You are not allowed to worry me like that ever again!
Hey, watch where you're aiming that thing!
Well, look who's here.
So you finally came out to play.
Well, you didn't leave me much of an option.
Spoken like a true coward.
It's been a long time.
Whaddya say we do some catching up?
In my torture chamber.
Thanks, but I'm not really into that stuff.
I think I'll pass.
I'm glad you set up those
charges before you left, Lubbock.
We didn't plan this, but they're being put to good use!
I'd never suspect you'd enter the fray
without a strategy. It's so much fun.
You must be here to rescue your
little partner, eh, Night Raid?!
Let's go!
Understood.
You handle General Budo for me, okay?
What? But how am I supposed to
fight a guy with hair like that?
Revolutionary filth like you should never be
permitted to set foot inside the sacred coliseum!
Prepare to be destroyed by my Imperial Arms!
Since you won't surrender...
You must die.
Is that your Imperial Arms?
It is.
I am Susanoo.
I don't care what it's called.
It won't need a name... after this!
Back off!
Very nice! Keep it up!
Man, you'd be easier to save if you weren't so damn tiny!
Do you really think this is
the time to start picking on me?
Look out!
Ow, that hurt!
You must be their close-range fighter!
Take the shot, hurry!
If she does, it'll surely kill you too!
Oh no, my healing ability is pretty badass.
Guess I have to trust you!
I didn't expect it to paralyze my whole body!
An impressive team you have here.
First that young man on the crucifix, and now you two.
It's regrettable that you've chosen
the path of wickedness and treason.
Who cares what you think?!
Whether it's the right one or not, the
path will be my own, thank you very much!
Mine!
Oh really now? You finished already?
Clearly, you don't realize what my weapon can do.
This is my Adventurous Bunker Pumpkin.
And its firepower gets deadlier
the more dangerous the situation!
It's to my advantage to have my back up against the wall!
The greater the threat, the stronger I get!
It's not charged enough yet!
You're not getting through!
Found it!
Hang in there, Tatsumi.
Now freeze.
Susanoo!
What a shame. And to think I used to
have so much respect for you as a general.
I hope you have more to offer.
Why was I saving my energy?
This is Esdeath I'm dealing with!
Magatama Manifest!
What are you up to?
Night Raid must be more resilient than
you think if we've survived this long.
Even if he is frozen solid, I
wouldn't let my guard down just yet.
Are you ready now, Susanoo?
It's time to defeat Esdeath!
Must be your trump card. This should be good.
But it won't be enough to overpower me.
You must realize that you're outmatched!
Eight-Handed Mirror Shield!
She always has something.
Man, this guy's annoying!
Look out, he's gaining on you!
Don't worry, Tatsumi!
I know it looks pretty serious from where you are,
but I'm getting ready to turn the
tables on this loser and save you!
Well then, it appears you possess everything
it takes to master that Imperial Arms.
It seems to be fluently
resonating with your every emotion!
Eat this!
Either way, you're not going to win!
You're about to eat those words, you pile of crap!
Mine, no!
I'm okay, Tatsumi.
Don't you remember? I made a promise to myself,
I was gonna make something of my life, didn't I?
My strength... is Pumpkin's strength!
I'm not finished yet!
Out of mercy, I'll go ahead
and put you out of your misery.
I don't need mercy from you.
All of my people are going to
walk out of this place alive.
I'm not losing any more friends! I'm not!
Allow me to demonstrate the ultimate
power of Adramelech's trump card!
Solid Shooter!
This is bad!
Mine, don't!
Please, Pumpkin... Please.
Channel my feelings!
Say goodbye, little girl!
Tatsumi!
YOU CAN'T KILL ME!
What? No!
I... won...
Hold on!
Tatsumi!
Mine!
Please... not this!
Oh no...
The mission's complete!
Get back to base, NOW!
Tatsumi, I won't let you leave!
Sacred Sword of the Heavens!
I gotcha!
Everything in sight will be encased in ice.
Mahapadma!
That ability puts such enormous strain on me,
I'm not capable of using it as often as I'd like.
Too much would be overkill, anyway.
What... what happened?
Esdeath, what did you do?!
Oh, I just froze time and space.
It's my special trump card that I
developed for just such an occasion.
I wanted something that would not only keep
Tatsumi from escaping, but effectively slay my enemies.
SUSANOO, GET OUT OF THERE!
I suppose I should congratulate
you for inspiring me to use it.
Susanoo's core!
You lose.
Now if you'll accompany me to the torture chambers...
What?! Impossible!
It's regenerating itself!
This makes three times. It's our last shot.
It'll take everything I have left.
If I exhaust my life force,
I'm sure I can make him even more powerful.
If General Budo is dead, then my life was well spent.
I can die peacefully knowing that.
The rest is up to you, Susanoo.
Burn in Hell, Najenda!
Celestial Treasure Magatama!
Well, he just boosted his power.
Su, let me help you!
Run away, Tatsumi.
But he's powered up now!
It's just the way his attacks overlapped.
It's making it appear as though
Susanoo's strength increased by double.
But the level he is right now, he'll
never even come close to defeating Esdeath.
Su!
It looks like you've gotten tougher,
but you're still not strong enough.
Despite your best efforts, you're still losing this fight.
Don't do it!
Please try not to forget the reason
we came here in the first place.
Run, Tatsumi.
But, Su...
In my thousand years as an Imperial Arms, my time
with this group has been the most fun I've ever had.
I have no regrets.
Susanoo...
I bid you farewell.
Stop right there!
I don't think so!
That mirror again.
I will never let you catch up to them!
So you're using yourself as a shield in
order to buy time for your companions to escape.
Where does Najenda find all these mushy little softies?
I am nothing more than a weapon.
And now I have no trump card.
Given my situation, wouldn't you agree
that this is my best possible option?
You said your name was Susanoo, yes?
So you WERE listening.
I will forever remember it as the name of a
legendary warrior, and NOT an Imperial Arms.
Now, as you face your demise, I will enjoy watching
your sad attempts to avoid your inevitable end!
We're going back to the base.
Just hang in there!
You'll be all healed up in no time.
Put me down.
Don't be an idiot.
Your injuries are serious.
Just do it, okay?
Tatsumi?
I'm right here.
Ever since you saved me back in Kyoroku,
I've been trying to find a way to repay you.
That's why I...
No... You didn't have to do that!
We can... call it even now.
Yeah, sure! We're even. Just
don't give up on me, all right?!
You're so stupid.
I can't just heal myself like Leone does.
I wanted to be...
I wanted to be by your side 'til the end.
Don't talk like that!
'Cause we're supposed to be... together...
Together forever!
You're such a bad liar, Tatsumi.
And you're... the biggest crybaby I ever met.
I can't believe you...
Why did you have to save me?
If it meant you were gonna...
You can't just...
A man... should never let anyone see him cry.
Hey...
Tatsumi?
Yeah?
I'm glad I...
I'm glad I fell in love with you.
Mine...
You can't die...
PLEASE don't die!
You have to survive and make
something of your life, right?!
What are you talking about?
I already... I already did.
I love... you.
Mine...
Mine, no!
Mine!