Is this some sort of dream?
Nope... unfortunately this is not a dream.
Huh? Looks like someone's coming up from the valley.
He's pretty fast too!
Who is this guy?!
They practically wiped out all of Stylish's creations!
I should probably hide for now.
Tatsumi's not back yet.
I'm starting to get a really bad feeling.
Hello, Imperial Capital?
So good to be back! Hehe...
Hehe... I'd know your scent
anywhere; Good to see you Tatsumi!
So tell me why you ran away. I've missed you so much.
Wha?! What're you doing here?!
Silly boy. I'm here to capture the
Danger Beasts attacking the Capital.
Uh... Which leads me to the question of why you're here.
Uh!
She's onto me!
I'm dead if I can't come up with something good.
Oh yeah about that, um, before I tell you
do you think maybe you could let go of me?
I will not.
Um, please it makes me nervous
when we're close together like this.
I'm not letting you go.
Uh... I'm testing myself!
I heard that there were some
Danger Beasts on the mountain!
A man after my own heart.
Well? Did you join the Revolutionary Army yet?
Uh...
No, not yet.
But I'm still planning to enlist as soon as I can.
I guess you could say that's the reason
I'm out here trying to hone my skills.
Yes. I see that.
Judging by the amount of muscle you've built up
I'd wager your abilities have exponentially grown.
You've obviously been working hard!
And with so much room to improve!
You really think so?
I do not have time for any of this!
The Danger Beasts are almost all gone.
They have really been a nuisance...
But honestly, thanks to them we're together again!
Love is a strange thing!
Uh, eh...
How can there be so many
interruptions on a deserted mountain?
You there!
The coward trying to hide.
Show yourself.
If you refuse, you'll get no mercy from me!
Well shit, I thought you wouldn't notice me.
Not too shabby.
Now I understand why everyone
is so bloody terrified of you.
Anyway, now that the two of us
have finally exchanged pleasantries...
it's probably a good time for me
to stop playing with my little toys.
Sounds like you know something about
why Danger Beasts are roaming this area.
I'd be more than glad to torture it out of you.
Sorry madam, but that's not my cup of tea.
But if you're in need of a little excitement
I'm willing to let you play with my toys as well!
Behold my Imperial Arms!
Shambala!
What's happening?!
Now then...
I wonder what kind of game we should play next.
Uhhh...
Where are we?!
Uh.. Miss Esdeath...
could you hit me really hard?
Tatsumi... I didn't know you were into that.
We really are perfect for each other, isn't it wonderful?
Oh god, that's not what I meant!
I just want to find out if that guy trapped
us in some kind of illusion, that's all!
So if you were to hurt me, maybe
I'd snap out of it, you know?!
Understood.
As you wish.
Uh!
Mmm...
It's not an illusion.
Our surroundings feel too real.
The cool breeze blowing on the waves...
The warm sunshine...
Everything around us is true.
Then what happened?
I assume this was somehow caused by that man we saw.
How did he manage to teleport us?
That can't be possible, right?!
The Empire has 48 legendary
weapons known as Imperial Arms.
Rumor has it that the secret art of a lost nation was
used to create one that could manipulate space itself.
Uh! That's crazy!
Wait, hang on.
Isn't that basically what Incursio
does every time I summon its armor?
Oh man...
when I think about it like that it kinda freaks me out!
Of all the Imperial Arms, I can only think
of a handful with the power to control space.
Who was that man?
Let's take a look around.
Ah!
Oh crap, there's nothing but ocean!
But isn't this a gorgeous view?
It's starting to feel kind of like
we're on a date, isn't it, my darling?
I'd rather start with dinner first.
You never know what can happen
when dealing with Imperial Arms.
In my line of work you have
to be able to adapt immediately.
I'm sure you do.
Now, where were we?
Right, we're on a date! Wanna cuddle?
Hey, stop it!
Well he's a big fella.
It looks just like Dr. Stylish
after he used that trump card!
Even with everyone in Night Raid working
together, it was still a close fight!
Do the two of us even stand a chance?
He's after us!
I won't let him ruin our time together.
You are interrupting!
You deserve to be impaled!
Weiss Schnabel!
She's even stronger than I thought.
You're still standing.
This is getting interesting.
Hey... you see that weird spot on his forehead?
Doesn't it look kinda weak?
I was thinking the same thing.
We must be soulmates!
Grau Horn!
He's quite stubborn.
Ahhhhh!
Tatsumi?!
Ah!
Well done!
Though I had originally planned on
winning your heart with my own skills...
you wound up deepening my love for you.
And here I used some of my favorite moves and everything!
There's another one!
Leave it to me, Tatsumi, I'll give him what he deserves!
Hagel Sprung!
Heh!
Wow, I cannot believe the size of that attack.
She's on a whole different level.
So this is how General Esdeath fights.
Akame... how the heck are you going to kill her?!
Those two must have been the last of them.
So that was what he meant by "picking up his toys."
Which means this was where he was
hiding that new breed of Danger Beast.
So what do you want to do after our break?
First we'll explore the area so we can
develop a better understanding of our situation.
Good idea.
We still don't know what we're dealing with.
We'll only make things worse if we panic.
It's best to remain calm.
You're right! Let's get to work!
Wait, did I really just say that?
She's the enemy, remember?!
Mmm... not quite right.
We searched the island for so long the sun went down huh.
Yes... and it's been a lovely time.
Uh... oh, yeah.
Not only that,
but I also managed to figure out where we are.
Oh!
This island is several miles
to the southeast of the Empire.
What? You've gotta be kidding me.
Wow, I had no idea we were so far away.
Which means...
You and I are the only two people on this island, Tatsumi.
So, then... what would you like to do?
You're in charge. Go ahead, choose your fate.
Well, don't all those options mean about the same thing?!
Aw, you're no fun at all.
How can you be so calm and easy-going about this?
Of course I'm calm;
I'm the one who knows how to get back.
Don't worry.
Huh?!
However, I'll need you to give me your full cooperation.
Is that clear?
Uh, yeah!
I've got a really bad feeling about this.
But if things get chaotic I might
have a chance to make a break for it.
All I can do is hope!
Just as I thought, the secret
was in where he transported us.
So, does that mean he can only teleport
to places that have this mark?
Based on the size of the light when it activated,
I'd say it only works on a few people at a time.
And it must use a large amount of
energy, so he can't do it very often.
So you think.. If we stay by this spot...
The gate should open again eventually.
But this is only the first way I found.
Now. Before I tell you the second way
back, there's something I'd like to do.
Sure, what is it?
Now that we're all by ourselves,
let's learn more about each other.
Whoa whoa whoa, time out!
If that's all you want then
there's a lot of other ways to do it!
Want me to stop?
Okay. Then you have to answer my questions.
First off: Where did you learn to fight with a sword?
Uh, well, there was this veteran
who used to live in my village.
Apparently he was a pretty good martial arts teacher.
Anyway, I trained under him.
Interesting.
Did he teach you about blacksmithing as well?
I tried to master as many skills as
I could so I'd make a lot of money.
To accomplish something like that takes
a lot of diligence. You're very talented!
I, uh, get the feeling that you
could accomplish just about anything.
Not true. For example, I'll never
have an appreciation of say, the arts.
The first time I heard Nyau play the flute,
I couldn't understand what was so special.
This could be my chance to
get some information out of her.
I mean, she's crazy about me, how hard can it be?
Maybe I can find something in our conversation
that'll help me convince her to join our side.
To fight for us.
Let's face it...
I'd much rather have her as a friend than a foe!
So uh, Miss Esdeath..
You didn't grow up in the Capital, did you?
That's right.
I was born close to the Northern border.
I don't suppose you've heard of the Partas clan?
I haven't.
They were a hunting clan that
specialized in killing Danger Beasts.
And I was the daughter of their chief.
Since you were kind enough to tell me
about your past.. I guess I'll share mine.
Father! I caught my prey!
Ah! Well done!
You're a good little hunter for your age...
but I think your old-man's got you beat!
Wow!
We're about to begin the butchering process.
Are ya ready?
Mm-hm...
I went ahead and weakened it.
And it's tied down so it can't hurt us.
But let's be quick just in case, okay?
It hurts my ears when they scream like that.
Yeah, I can't do much for the pain, but the
eggs are more valuable if the beast is still alive.
Y'see, it used to survive by devouring our people.
Not anymore, this time the predator loses.
The hunter may have been strong,
but in this case the hunted ended up being
just a little bit stronger in the end.
It's what it deserves for being weaker than me.
Esdeath. Carve out the eyes and the crest.
Mm-hm...
I'll do my best, Father!
She never hesitates to kill a target,
even if it's weak or trying to run away.
She's a natural hunter.
But that being said...
I can't help but wonder if she's missing something.
I can only hope it won't be a problem.
Eat or be eaten.
That's the kind of wonderful
lifestyle in which I was raised.
It was just us and the Danger Beasts.
The way both sides desperately
fought for their lives was so much fun.
Oh, an insect war?
Yeah.
It seems to me like the fighting's already over.
Look over there, the enemy soldiers
have dragged the queen out of the fortress
and they're getting ready to lynch her.
That's what happens to the weak, right?
Yes, Esdeath.
This situation is exactly the same as it was
when your mother was eaten by the Danger Beast.
Make no mistake, this is how the world works.
It may be sad, but your mother died because she was weak.
The strong survive; The weak become prey.
Camping in the mountains these past few days paid off!
I caught this guy all by myself!
Father is gonna be so proud of me!
What happened...?
What's going on?!
The northern tribe just came from across
the border and started attacking our people.
The chief took charge and
killed a few dozen of the bastards,
but then they ganged up on him all
at once and he couldn't hold 'em off.
Father!
Esdeath...
it's like I've told you...
We were defeated because we weren't strong enough.
This was our fate.
Never let yourself be of the weak, Esdeath.
Never become the prey.
I continued to hunt Danger Beasts on my own,
but eventually I ran out of prey,
so I became an Imperial officer.
So somewhere along the line I switched
from preying on monsters to targeting humans.
And well, that's my story.
I get it.
You wanted revenge on the northern tribe.
I can understand why you hated them so much.
Hmm? I suppose that's what it must look like...
but I don't necessarily hate them.
What?
Well then what about all those rumors of
you burying hundreds of northerners alive?
I wanted to be efficient when I made an example of them.
Besides, I would have done that
regardless of what my feelings were.
I couldn't disobey orders, you know.
Huh?
What happened to my father was regrettable, but
it doesn't change the fact that he was a weak man.
Is there anything else you wanted to ask me?
I'm more than willing to tell you
whatever you want to know, Tatsumi.
Uhh... actually...
I was kinda wondering if maybe I could
see what your Imperial Arms looks like.
Oh, that?
My Imperial Arms...
Ahh...
Look.
It's right here.
What?!
It happened several years ago.
Hmm... I've offered a variety of weapons,
but your affinity seems poor with all of them.
Well, I am impressed with how enormous
this axe is... but nothing's caught my eye.
Huh?
Is that an Imperial Arms in that urn over there?
Yes, the Demon's Extract.
The blood of an S-Class Danger-Beast from the far north.
A blood-type weapon?
The legends say if you drink the
extract and it resonates properly,
you'll be able to obtain the Danger
Beast's ability to manipulate ice.
However, every warrior to attempt to
do so has lost his mind in the process.
That all sounds rather fascinating, doesn't it?
You're not going to drink that!
You may have a dangerous reputation,
but that doesn't mean it'll bond with you!
I feel so drawn to it...
as if it's beckoning me to drink.
That's a good sign.
Perhaps the Extract is right for you.
Maybe.
For some reason I feel certain I was meant for this.
I honed my intuition out in the wild;
If I'm wrong, I deserve to die.
It should only take a sip to know for sure.
No reason not to drink the whole thing.
I bet that'll make me even stronger.
I guess it can't drive you insane if you already are.
Ahh...
My, that tasted so...
Gah!
Huh?!
Kill! Steal! Murder!
Destroy! Humiliate!
Break! Slaughter!
Hehe... haha...
The urge to destroy is overwhelming!
Now I understand why everyone else went crazy...
but I will not!
This is nothing!
I won't be bested by a mere goblet of blood!
I will always be on top.
I will always be victorious...
no matter what gets in my way!
And I will answer to no one but myself!
I'm feeling truly delightful now, Minister.
The power's surging through my entire body.
You seem to have already merged.
To the birth of the world's most powerful warrior...
Esdeath!
So after all this time that
monster's blood is still in your body?
That's correct.
But I mastered it long ago, you don't need to worry.
So that's what made you like to torture people?
Oh, no.. I've always enjoyed that.
She didn't do it for revenge,
and it's not because that Demon's
Extract thing makes her go berserk.
Either of those would've been better than this.
She's been true to herself from the very beginning...
nothing could change someone with a personality like that!
I can't believe I was gonna try to win her over again!
I'm such an idiot!
Hmm.
I wonder how those two are doing.
I'm sure they haven't gotten themselves killed yet.
Perhaps it's about time I re-opened the portal, yes?
Shambala Point B, release.
That oughta do it.
Hmm... What are you doing over there?
Huh? Excuse me, bitch?
You know, despite your language,
you seem oddly... refined.
Ha, well, no shit.
I mean, Minister Honest is my father, so...
Huh, that man is your father?
Grrr...
Guh...
What the hell does a whore have to say about it, huh?!
I happen to have great respect for
him... but I can do far better than he has.
I consider surpassing your parents to be
a good show of filial piety, don't you?!
So uh...
about that second way back you found...
Oh yes, I'm sure I can tell you now.
We just need to secure a ride.
There are quite a few species of Danger
Beasts that will let you ride on their backs.
Although.. Sometimes it's a little
difficult to train them not to throw you off.
You'd better let me do it.
Wait, isn't that one up there?
Huh? I guess it is.
That's too bad. Be right back.
Wait, what? How are you planning on catching it?
It's way too far up in the sky!
I'll train it after I shoot it down!
Just watch!
Whoa, it opened!
This is my perfect chance to get outta here!
Hmm...
But, she did look after me this whole time.
I should return the favor.
Look, Miss Esdeath!
The portal's opening up again!
I'm going through, okay?!
Ah! Tatsumi, wait!
Don't go in there!
This is the same mountain we were on yesterday.
Tatsumi, are you here?
Did he really get that far
ahead of me in those few seconds?
Impossible, he didn't have that much time.
Even though I'm invisible,
she'll feel my aura if I move.
All I can do now, is wait 'til she leaves.
He's not here.
Could it be... he was sent to another location?
I lost him again.
But one thing is certain...
now that we've found each other a second time,
I'm sure it won't be the last.
Fate will bring you back to me... I can feel it.
I can feel it too.
But now, I know for sure I'll
never persuade you to join us.
So the next time the two of us meet...
it will be as enemies.