Whooo, alright!!
This feels awesome!
Hahaha... You're so innocent I can't
believe you're a killer, Tatsumi. It's funny.
I'd never expect that!
Wow! This is even more of a blast than I thought!
Yeah. The view is really something. This is nice.
This isn't nice at all!
The Marg Highlands are crawling with Danger Beasts,
which makes it impossible for humans to live here.
And that's why it's a perfect
place to build our new hideout.
The Revolutionary Army's recon unit is currently searching
for a more permanent place for us near the capital,
but they haven't found anything.
So until we hear from them we'll just
stay right here and level ourselves up.
Hey, look!
It's leaving; Should we try to catch it?
It's going back to its nest at HQ, silly!
Well, Mine, I'm surprised you
weren't smart enough to figure that out.
Hahaha...
Oh great. I hate you already!
Oh yes, I haven't given our
new members a proper introduction.
I'd like you to meet-Huh?
I already knew you were cute, but
you're adorable from up close, Akame!
Why are you touching me?
Oh, yes, my name's Chelsea.
Since we're going to be killing
people together, I hope we all get along.
Here! This is for you.
Oh!
Welcome to the team.
Did she just win Akame's heart with a lollipop?!
That long flight must have made her really hungry!
You know, Chelsea seems even less likely to be a
cold-blooded assassin than Mine and the others girls do.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
She's an expert killer who's
completed just as many jobs as Akame.
Eh?
As for this fellow, headquarters
has entrusted him with me as well.
Everyone meet the Lightning Fast Susanoo,
he's my new Imperial Arms.
Organic types are mostly autonomous,
so he shouldn't be all that draining.
Even with all my injuries I can still use him.
Uh... Hi, I think we met earlier.
Ah!
Uh, hey now...
Fixed!
I should warn you,
he's a bit of a neat freak.
Yeah, no kidding...
Well now I get why he fixed my hair before.
Okay. So, what exactly is his primary ability?
Does he only do hand-to-hand combat?
Hehe...
Allow me to demonstrate that for you.
Try to contain your excitement.
Susanoo, proceed!
Understood.
Okay I admit, that does look impressive, but...
what is he doing?
From where I'm standing it looks like... chores.
Wonderful, isn't he?!
Susanoo's original purpose was to
protect royalty and others of status.
Not only can he fight,
he's equipped with a full range of cleaning and
cooking skills so he never has to leave his owner's side!
He can do it all!
And the best part is, his menu
includes a thousand different dishes!
How is any of that gonna help us in a fight?!
Now, now, I'm sure you'll come to appreciate it.
Last but not least... he also
possesses a trump card for combat.
Don't you?
Yeah.
So these are my two new teammates, huh?
They seem pretty reliable.
Oh my goodness, you're flat as a board, aren't you?
Y'know, you may be all big and
handsome and strong and everything,
but you're still just a glorified man-maid!
Hope our teamwork isn't gonna suffer.
We've finished searching the doctor's residence.
However, we were unable to find any evidence
as to what caused his sudden disappearance.
We did notice none of his valuable research materials
or equipment went missing from the laboratory, though.
If he hasn't deserted us,
that means he must have been killed.
And none of his enhanced soldiers
were anywhere to be found either.
I can only assume they were all killed as well.
I understand.
Poor Seryu's lost another person she looked up to.
Are you going to be able to handle your
maintenance without the doctor's help?
I think I'll be alright!
He did leave all the materials I need in the laboratory.
I can't make any improvements to my equipment,
but I can keep them in working order!
That's good.
So, Seryu, tell me how Judgement-of-the-Ten-Kings
and your other new weapons have been working for you.
Great! I'm really enjoying them, Doctor!
I'm quite impressed with how well
your body handled the experiment.
Now use all that newfound power
to make your dreams come true.
And I'll be right here to fix you if you get a boo boo.
Ha...
Okay!
My parents...
Captain Ogre...
and the Doctor.
Everyone I care about gets killed...
and always by the same filth!
Seryu.
Commander... I...
I can't take it anymore!
All I want...
is to slaughter them all as soon as possible!
If you'll stay with me, Seryu,
I promise I will fulfill that wish.
You can count on it.
Thank you!
I swear, Commander...
I will dedicate everything I have to you, and to justice.
I know you will.
Here we go! I'm gonna find Seryu
and put a great big smile on her face!
And what makes you so sure you can do that?
It's something my mom told me one time.
If a girl's ever crying or acting upset
it's a man's job to make her feel better again!
Mm... Hmmm...
And this is one of those times.
Seryu, lay your troubles on me!
Ehh... haha...
Uh...
It looks like the Empire is gradually
beginning to build up its forces.
And there's no way we can win as we are now.
We have to make ourselves stronger.
Revolution Day is almost here.
Let's use what little time we have left for training.
I also wouldn't count on getting
any more new fighters if I were you.
Please consider this the last
time we receive reinforcements.
If we work as a team,
we can all survive to see the coming of the new world!
Hm.
Ah, got one!
Huh?
Much better.
It's gonna be a huge feast tonight! I can't wait!
Phew!
Ah man, that was delicious and hit the
spot, Su! I feel like I can take on the world!
Thank you for all your help.
Hey, Su, so you think we could train together tomorrow?
Hmm. I knew you'd come around
once you saw how handy he can be.
It is pretty cool that the guys back at Headquarters
would let you borrow such an awesome weapon.
They said Susanoo had been in
hibernation for quite some time.
He felt my presence, and activated immediately.
That's really cool.
Oh, it's easy to see why.
My feminine charm, of course.
Actually the General is like a
spitting image of my previous master.
That makes sense.
If she was like me, then she
must have been a wonderful person.
Yeah.
Not only a great leader, but also a good man!
A man?!
Gah...
Hahaha...
See, Boss, you totally look like a dude!
That's probably why you're such a stud!
Cut it out, if you make her mad
she's gonna freak out and kill us...
Oh! Uh... Yeah sorry.
Uh-oh...
Oww...
Jeez, I don't get why everybody's
so quick to cozy up to that guy.
I thought I was the Mr. Suave Awesome around here.
Don't worry, Lubb, I'm pretty sure no one
considered you "suave" in the first place.
Oh, wow.
Is that a baby panther cub?
They're surprisingly comfortable
around humans, aren't they?
Hey now, I'm not gonna share
my food with you or anything so-.
Uhh...
Okay... maybe just one bite.
Whoa!
Hehehe...
What a perfect little snack!
Whaa?! It's you?!
Hehehe... Oh, Mine, you always make it
so easy I just can't help myself! Mmm...
I hate you!
So that was your Imperial Arms?
It sure was! I can instantly
transform into anything I want!
Pretty cool, right?
Gaia Foundation, it's perfect for stealth operations.
Which I must say Mine, if you're not more careful, you'll
be the next team member to get killed on the battlefield.
Excuse me?! If the enemy finds out
about your weapon, then you're screwed!
Admittedly. It is a cosmetic-type Imperial
Arms, so I can't do any real damage with it.
But that's what makes the art of deception so exciting!
Like that look of surprise on your face a minute ago...
Makes it all worth it.
Ahhh! God I hate you!
Tatsumi, you take care of the little one!
You got it!
All their attacks do a lot of damage.
I need to study their movements...
avoid taking any direct hits...
and take 'em down!
Uh!
There it is.
Incursio's hidden polearm, Neuntote!
I don't know where it started...
But Tatsumi's really started to pull his own weight!
Heh!
He'll be right up there with Bulat one of these days.
Guh!
There's no end to these ugly little shits!
It's like they keep calling for backup or something.
The leader's gotta be around here somewhere.
Hot damn!
Nice try!
I guess that must be your trump card!
Huh?
Ha! Didn't even break a sweat!
Well done! You've proven you can easily
kill the Danger Beasts in this area.
I've noticed some of the different types like to attack us
out of nowhere, so we constantly have to be on our toes!
I like it! That makes it so much more interesting!
The air's pretty thin up here.
You've been training in such a harsh environment...
I'm sure all of you have leveled up quite a bit!
You're right! I can already feel a huge difference!
Chelsea.
Hm?
Tell me. What do you think of Night Raid
now that you've been with us for a month?
Hm. You're all strong.
In fact I would say you're even
stronger than anyone from my old team.
Ha!
Aw yeah! You got that right!
That said...
Just because you're strong doesn't mean you'll survive.
I took the liberty of looking
through all your old reports.
Sheele and Bulat were both killed in a recent battle.
The issue at hand isn't whether
or not they were good people.
It's that those two were obviously incompetent.
Hmm!
What?
All I'm trying to say is, if you don't get it together,
then you're not going to last long enough
to see this fight through to the end.
I swear...
That girl pisses me off so much!
Well, that's Chelsea for you;
She's as honest as they come.
We should eat something.
Let's go ahead and get a head-start
on cooking everything you hunted.
Can't work on an empty stomach.
There is something really wrong with you guys.
So, what did you want to talk about, Mine?
You know it had to make you mad.
I can't believe what she said about Sheele and Bulat!
Yeah, I understand.
I don't like it when people disrespect Bro.
We need to do something to
her that'll really screw her up.
Something that'll scare the crap out
of her or at least make her look stupid.
Here it is. You get her off her guard, really
shake her up, then I'll come in and deal the final blow!
It's total genius!
Why do I feel like nothing good can
possibly come from teaming up with you?
What do you mean?! Don't you dare tell me
that you're gonna take her side on this one?
You know she deserves it!
Okay, okay, fine, whatever you want.
But wait, you never explained how
you wanted me to surprise Chelsea.
Well, you and Lubb will have to
figure something out, won't you?
I've got my own brilliant revenge to prepare.
So get busy, this mission should be completed tonight!
And I'd better hear her scream too!
I don't think I like her tone.
Hmm... Something that'll make Chelsea scream...
I got nothin' over here.
If only we could use our Imperial Arms to startle people-.
OH! I think I just had an idea!
And it was a GOOD idea!
Whoaaa!
Never thought I'd use Incursio for this.
Listen up! It's almost time for Chelsea to take a bath,
so make sure you're ready!
You just need to go invisible and
sneak into the hot spring from the back.
As soon as you can get close enough... all you have
to do is grab the wash bucket and dump it over her head!
She's totally gonna freak out, it'll be great! I promise.
Hmm...
Are you sure this is a good idea?
Come on! Mine's practically forcing us
to do it, so we have the perfect excuse!
It's a once-in-a-lifetime chance!
Well, okay...
But I can't let you come with me.
You understand, right, Lubb?
Hm... That's cool!
I'll let you have the fun part!
You're the best!
This is perfect! Now I can gauge how mad Chelsea will get
at a peeping tom without having to get my own ass beat.
If she lets him off the hook,
maybe I can get away with it too!
I should just get this over with.
Otherwise I could spend the
whole night just staring at her.
Okay. Maybe for a second.
Alright, let's do this.
Ahhh! That's definitely a guy!
You can come out now. I know you're there.
Uh!
Su?! How'd you know?!
Incursio can make you invisible, but that's all it does.
You'll have to learn to hide your aura on your own.
Huh!
Always bear that in mind when you fight.
If you forget, it's over.
Uh-huh.
Huh.
You left yourself open!
Huh?! Wha... What?!
Haha...
Surprise ya? It was me the whole time!
Ahh...
Uh, you seriously need to work on
quelling that aura of yours, Tatsumi.
The moment I sensed it, I knew
I could turn the tables on you.
Oh yeah, I guess that's why you were
sitting here waiting for me then, huh?
You win this round!
Hehe... Deception is my specialty, you know.
To detect something like that
you'd need much more training.
I'm sorry, does it get on your nerves
when people tell you things like that?
Not really.
Hm?
I understand what you're saying, Chelsea.
There's still so many things I need to improve.
I promise I'll take your advice to heart.
So, you're pretty mature, aren't you?
The truth is...
Not too long ago I came back from a mission
only to discover that everyone on my team
had been murdered while I was gone.
I would be devastated if something like
that were to happen to the people here.
All I'm trying to say is if you don't get it together
then you're not going to last long
enough to see this fight through to the end.
The only reason she said all that stuff
was because she was concerned about us.
Hmm...
How about that?
You're a lot sweeter than I
thought you were when we first met.
Uhmm...
How dare you say that to me!
Just looking out for my mental
well-being like anybody would!
And the next time you try to sneak
a little peek at me when I'm naked...
I won't hesitate to cut it off, is that clear?
Uh... did you say "cut it off"?!
Cut what off?!
Uh...
Hmm, Commander?
Yeah?
Is there anything troubling you?
Whenever there's a large crowd, I
find myself searching for Tatsumi.
Actually...
If I may... I've compiled a list of eligible
bachelors who all bear some resemblance to that boy.
If it pleases you, I could set up some meetings.
There's no need to trouble yourself, Run.
There can only be one Tatsumi, after all.
No one else will ever come close.
My humblest apologies.
Hmm, this complicates things.
I knew she was sadistic and that she's
tasked with the Minister's dirty work.
But she's even more powerful and depraved than I imagined.
It should prove rather entertaining to
observe her up close for a little while.
Why do I feel so anxious?
Am I sensing that I'm about to see Tatsumi again?
Or is it because...
because the final battle against
Night Raid is drawing near.
Or perhaps, it's something else altogether!
Ahh! It's some new kind of Danger Beast!
Run!
Ahh!
Hehehe...
Looks like I got my hands on a fun little new toy!
Y'know, I haven't been to the Capital in ages...
Should be a wonderful time.