Oh God...
We may have celebrated a little too
hard last night for Tatsumi's return.
Guess we all crashed out here.
Sleepy, sleepy...
I've done it, Master Stylish!
Your trusty assistant Trauma has done iiiit!
Good work, now let's continue the mission.
He got the first one, Doctor Stylish.
Marvelous! That's my little knight in shining
armor, flying straight into enemy headquarters.
All right...
Go, Beautiful Team Stylish!
The Dapper Offensive is officially underway!
The soldiers have made their way into Night Raid's base.
Ah, let the show begin! I'm tingling with anticipation!
Holy crap!
Where'd they come from all of a sudden?!
They're already on top of us!
How the hell did they even get in?
The enemy... must be killed.
This is bad. I need to find the rest of the team, now!
It sounds like they got one.
Well, my enhanced fighters are more resilient than humans.
It takes serious finesse to put even a scratch on them.
Is there some kind of problem?
Not really. But they seem pretty resilient themselves.
You'd be amazed how many awesome tricks
I can do with this little bit of string.
Check this out! Hyah!
KYAH!!!!
All I have to do is bind them all together, and...
Voila!
So creative...
Saw that in a manga one time.
You wouldn't believe it, but those crazy things
are full of ideas of how to manipulate string.
Crap, another one.
Nope. More than one.
Ah, sorry I'm not so good with groups.
I think I'm just gonna pass on you guys, if that's cool.
Ah, dammit, they're pretty fast!
Stay behind me Lubbock.
Yeah, I can do that!
Nice one, Akame!
Wait!
You want some too?!
Impressive for a couple of thugs.
He's strong.
You can call me Toby.
And I'm here to battle you one-on-one, Akame!
This one's different.
I felt it when I attacked. His entire body is mechanical!
Akame!
Giants, huh?
Okay!
Hey, you in the tin can!
Nice of you to show yourself.
Seems you're the fella I'm s'posed
to kill, so let's get down to it!
Those scissors!
Oh, these? The Shears of Creation Extase.
Just picked these up.
Give those back.
They don't belong to you!
These babies'll cut anything!
Pretty good reflexes boy. I
was gonna take your whole arm off!
No matter how thick that armor
is, I can cut right through it.
So, how's it feel to know your
armor is useless against me?
Your little outfit won't do you any good!
Sounds like we have the upper
hand over Murasame AND Incursio.
Exactly how I planned it.
It's easy to defeat somebody
you have a strong aversion to.
But still, we've already lost quite a few soldiers.
There's too much noise in the area
for me to determine the exact number,
but the death count is extremely high.
Oh dear, what a tragedy.
Just kidding!
Those silly pawns are wonderfully dispensable.
They're just criminals anyway.
Poor dolts are always happy to cut a deal with
me if they think it'll shorten their sentence!
Little do they know,
they're nothing but fancy fodder waiting to die!
Those belong to Sheele!
Give 'em to me NOW!
Huh? Who the hell is Shell?
You must really feel like dying today.
How about I start cuttin' some stuff off?
Real brave, picking on a pipsqueak.
Huh?
You're even more pathetic than I thought.
Mine!
So those pieces of crap couldn't handle
you by yourself, and now it's my job?!
I'm ready to get this over with.
Seeing Extase in your big, ugly
hands is starting to piss me off.
So you wanna get this over with?
Be careful what you ask for,
cause you're gonna get it, sweetie!
In case you haven't noticed, we took over your base!
You've been made, and it's all but done!
That's why I'll make it quick.
Do you know who you're talking to?!
Stupid little girl!
She knows I was able to withstand Incursio's attacks!
What's she gonna do with that pea-shooter?
Nooooo...
The more intense my fight,
the more intense my weapon.
You should not have underestimated me.
You're coming home, Sheele.
Kaku has been defeated.
And they've almost finished off the whole infantry.
Oh my goodness gracious, what a tragic turn of events.
I'm afraid that does it. Time for Plan B.
Doctor, there's something flying over us.
Huh?
That must be Danger Beast Air Manta!
And someone's riding on its back.
Wait a second...
It's ex-General Najenda!
Looks like she's got two other people with her, too.
Oooh, delightfully dramatic!
Valiantly riding on a Danger Beast she tamed herself?!
Now don't get yourself all worked up!
Headquarters was proud of their fortune-telling Arms.
It predicted trouble near the hideout,
and it came to pass.
Glad I flew back as soon as I found out.
This is your shot, recruits.
Time to show me what you're made of!
Well, isn't THIS a fun surprise?
It actually works out great for me.
Every one of you is going to become
a test subject for my experiments!
It's time to unveil my trump card!
If I can't finish you in a single hit,
then I'll have to chop you into pieces.
And it's gonna hurt. You better get ready.
That's where you're mistaken.
Given my condition, I can't feel pain anymore!
Hyah!
Yah!
Damn you! This wasn't even your fight!
My home and all of my friends are in danger.
Do you honestly expect me to just sit back and watch?
Well... As it was going, I
would have lost that battle anyway,
even if he hadn't interfered.
Akame... please tell me...
Why was it impossible for me to win against you?
Your fighting style was extremely aggressive,
but you left me too many openings.
Obviously.
I should've focused more on defense. Right?
A sense of pain is quite the useful luxury after all.
What is that?
More enemies?
Hang on, I'll check.
Whaddya know?! It's the boss!
Sweet, perfect timing! Wait, that's not fair!
What's not fair?
How come they get to ride on a giant fish?!
I wanna ride a fish!
Umm... I'm not sure I know exactly how to respond to that.
Oh, you adorable little lady!
You seem to have left yourself wide open!
You really caught me off-guard didn't you?
I was passed out and hung over
and you throw a knife at me?
That is grounds for a serious ass-kicking my friend!
Put me down! I can't breathe!
Word of advice.
I'm a huge fan of surprise attacks, but if there's
one thing I hate about them, it's when they happen to me!
Your body looks like it's been enhanced, but I
wouldn't expect that to make your death come any easier!
A-ha!
Well, she's just full of surprises isn't she?
Ow... He did manage to get in a
good one, and man does it hurt!
Oops! Oh crap!
I think I killed him.
Um... Sis?
You're okay now, right?
Yeah, he just surprised me at first, that's all.
But I can regenerate pretty fast when
I'm in my beast form, so I'll be just fine!
Everybody okay?
Yeah!
Good, I think we're all here.
Looks like we've still got some work to do.
This doesn't make sense. How did they
get in without setting off my traps?!
I'm not picking up anyone else's smell either.
Whatever, we're all together so
let's just knock these losers out, okay?
Right!
Akame!
Wha... what's wrong with you guys?!
I can't... move my body... argh!
This sensation... it's just
like what happened on that boat!
Hypnosis, maybe?
No... I think...
it's... it's...
Seems to be working perfectly on all
targets except the one wearing Incursio.
That's the effect of my trump card.
A fast-acting paralysis agent
I made all by my stylish self.
Aaah! But won't our allies be poisoned too?!
Obviously, the good doctor remembered
to treat them with the antidote, moron.
Oooh, Master Stylish, you're like a super genius!
It's not like I intended to try out my latest
concoction on such promising subjects, you know?
See? It's a very valuable creation
and I went to great lengths to make it!
But I had no other option!
They were wiping out my lovely cohorts so quickly!
We understand, Master!
You're so kind!
Yes, and the poison has no smell, so it's easy on my nose!
I'm holding up better than anyone else right now.
So it's all up to me!
Is he... with us?
Now! Exterminate every foe you see, Susanoo!
Understood.
What... the...
Sir! One of them has jumped down and
is now pulverizing the entire infantry!
But that's impossible, the poison should
affect every living being in the area!
Maybe not. He might have an unlisted Imperial Arms.
In which case, I guess I don't really
need to include him in my research.
Oops!
Do you like my deluxe human explosive?!
Ha! One down!
Oh my god... don't tell me...
I've only heard of these.
He's an organic.
He's a human Imperial Arms!
Um... what are you...
Fixed.
Wait, what?
Whoever did this found a spot
where he could easily spy on everyone.
He's probably hiding somewhere
upwind so the poison can't get to him.
If there's somebody calling the shots from above...
then he must be somewhere over...
There!
Susanoo! They're on the cliff to the southeast!
Don't let them get away!
Understood.
We've been discovered sir!
Nothing to be done, is there?
All we can do now is run!
Poison doesn't affect organic types!
You must either destroy the
core or immobilize the wielder!
My, my, she's even more tenacious than I thought!
There's nothing to be afraid of, Master Stylish!
We are your guardians until the bitter
end! I promise you're in good hands!
Oh, please, you don't stand a chance.
I designed you three for recon, not hand-to-hand combat.
Now that it's come to this...
I'll have to protect myself!
And play my second trump card, Danger
Beast Shot! Sorry, but you leave me no choice!
You okay, Master Stylish?
What's wrong?
Sir?
Oh, what an impeccable sensation!
This is the ultimate in nouveau riche!
I've successfully merged my body with a
Danger Beast, so I may personally kick your ass!
He is GORGEOUS!
Very impressive, Master!
But first I'm going to need a little sustenance, yes?
Time for us to become one!
Just as I expected, scarfing down all
this nutritious meat is helping me level up!
What is that thing?!
He's a mutation.
And he's totally gross!
Well this isn't bad,
but I'd still like to be a scoche bigger.
That Imperial Arms guy got me
pressed even when I'm a giant!
I suppose if I truly desire to win this battle,
I'll have to grow even larger!
Prepare yourself, to be devoured alive!
Interesting.
Oh crap, I'd better go help him!
Wait! Tatsumi...
I can't walk, but I need you to take me with you, okay?
Akame?
Sure!
You might wanna hold on tight.
Now, let's do this!
Where are you going, Mr. Fancy Pants?
Are you too afraid to attack me?
And you two! Playing some piggyback?
I'm sorry. But that's just tacky!!
You're wasting your time, darling!
The One-Hit Killer Murasame won't do
much good if it can't pierce my skin!
Now, perhaps it's time to give up...
Damn you!
You've lost all your little pawns.
You do know its almost over, don't you?!
I'm not done yet!
I bet you can reach his flesh from here!
Go for it, Akame!
You're done.
No... there were still so many people
on which I wanted to experiment...
I... I never thought it would end for me this way.
I pictured more panache.
You were lucky to die with all your parts intact.
Don't take something like that for granted.