Nothing but bad things happen to me.
The whole world can fall apart, for all I care.
Sis, I gotta go to the toilet.
Yuuki.
YUUKI!
BROKEN WORLD
What do I do?
Don't just stand there! You idiot!
Yu... Yuuki?
Excuse me...
A little boy...
Have any of you seen a little boy?
He must still be...
in the rest room.
Yuuki?
Yuuki!
The exit's this way!
Please, keep calm and keep moving!
You! Come back! It's dangerous that way!
You there! Girl! Come back!
You can't go that way!
The quake started a fire in that section.
Now get out through the west entrance!
But... But I... I have to...
A quake...
That was close, wasn't it?
I guess that's what they call "safe by a hair".
Thank you very much...
Aren't you the girl I just...?
Can you stand?
You're alone?
Where's your little brother?
I let him go to the rest room by himself.
What about your dad and mom?
My brother and I came here by ourselves.
I have to find him.
You're a good sister.
I let him go to the rest room by himself...
Did you look there?
But he was gone!
His name?
Huh?
What's your brother's name?
Yuuki.
Yuuki? Yuuki!
Well, come on. Let's find your brother.
Yuuki!
Yuuki?
Yuuki, are you here?
They're hurt.
Yeah. This earthquake was incredible.
Yuuki...
Excuse me.
Have you seen a little boy by himself?
He'd be about 7 or 8.
I have seen boys, but...
They were all with their parents.
Sorry I can't be of any more help you.
No, that's okay. Thanks.
Excuse me, have you seen a little boy by himself?
About this tall, maybe 7 or 8?
Excuse me! He was wearing a pea-green
T-shirt. It had a line going across his chest!
He's... He's my little brother!
I'm sorry, I haven't seen him.
I saw a few boys down in the
toy shop on the first floor, but...
You did?! Thank you so much!
Wait!
Let's look for another stairway.
This one seem too dangerous.
No! Come back!
Wait!
Come on.
Look, Sister... Don't do anything that reckless again.
Will you?
You know how dangerous that was, don't you?
But, Yuuki's in the toy shop!
I know! But what's the point if
you get yourself hurt, too?
"If I get hurt too?"
You don't say that!
You don't know that Yuuki is hurt.
You don't know that he is hurt!
Stop! It's dangerous that way!
Stop!
No! Let me go!
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
spoken to you that way.
Your little brother's all right. He's all right...
I'll help you find him, just stop being so reckless.
Yuuki?
Yuuki!
We've almost got it!
Okay... Lift!
Yuuki?!
YUUKI!
Are you okay? Is anyone hurt?
We're fine. Please, this place is dangerous.
You should both evacuate quickly.
Please, we're looking for a little boy.
He's wearing a pea-green shirt.
We've searched the whole place already.
This child is the last one.
The rest are...!
Yuuki! Where are you?!
Answer me, Yuuki!
Yuuki! Yuuki!
Sister... Let's get out of here.
It's dangerous here.
Come on, while the smoke isn't too thick.
No!
Go by yourself if you're leaving!
I won't leave Yuuki behind!
Then consider this!
Can you afford to let yourself get killed?!
If Yuuki's alive, he's trying
to get out of here, too!
That's why you mustn't die!
Stay alive, and you'll find him, right?!
Yuuki...!
Oh, after you're done, buy us a drink!
A drink! Hey wait!
Where are you going?!
Just let me check in here!
Come on.
Is someone there?
Help me! Over here! Help me, please!
W-We're coming!
Sis?
Sis, is that you?
Yuuki!
Sis!
Yuuki! Are you hurt?!
I'm okay.
Just hang on! I'll get you out of there in a second!
'Kay...
Grab that side!
Right!
Sis!
Yuuki! Yuuki!
Thank you so much.
Thank God, you're okay! Thank God...
Sis...
It's raining...
Do we wait till it lets up?
It's dangerous here.
Let's keep moving.
A fire?
Emm..
Hi, Yuuki.
Maybe we can stay out of the rain here.
Right.
Thank goodness.
Yeah.
Can't get through?
No luck here, either.
The release in Ohmoto were probably destroyed.
To repeat...
today at 3:45 PM,
approximately four hours ago
a massive earthquake occurred,
centered in the Kanto region.
The quake's epicenter was in the
northern area of Tokyo Bay,
at a depth of approximately 25 kilometers.
The scale of the earthquake
is estimated at magnitude 8.0...
Magnitude 8!
Please be careful of aftershocks and possible tsunamis.
C'mon. We can watch it on here.
Your phone works?
According to the Tokyo fire department, large
scale fires have broken out in all sections of the city.
I wonder if Dad and Mom are okay...
Where do you live? Close by?
Near Kinuta Park.
Oh, around Seijo, huh?
I live in Sangenjaya.
Dammit, I can't get through at all!
The only thing working is the one sag network.
Let's wait a little longer and see what develops.
They may give us an idea about
how we can all get home.
Why are you being so nice to us anyway?
I don't know...
Because it's human?
Or some such?
Your big sister here went
half crazy trying to find you.
She's a good sister, huh?
Thank you!
We have to get you home soon so
you can give that to your mom.
I just realized. I still haven't told you my name.
I'm Mari, Mari Kusakabe.
And you're Yuuki and...?
Mirai Onozawa.
Oh, Mirai, huh? That's a good name.
I don't like it much.
Well, I like your name, Sis. It's pretty.
Oh.
You're in middle school?
Seventh grade.
How about you, Yuuki?
Third grade!
Coming out here all by yourselves...
You must be very close.
Not really...
It's all her mother's fault that this happened anyway.
Everything with her is always work.
She's the one who told me to take him here.
That's kind of harsh, isn't it?
I live at home with my mother and daughter,
but I work so much,
I hardly have time for my little girl.
She loves to play on the swings,
so she said she wants me to work hard,
so we can move to a house with one.
But if I don't hurry,
she might end up too old to sit on a swing.
That's right.
I have a little something to get.
I left it on my bike near here.
That one, might not come back.
She's not coming back, is she?
She left us here.
She doesn't have any
obligation to take care of us.
It's okay.
They're called aftershocks.
You get a bunch of them like
this after a major quake.
That was a little one just now.
I'm sure we're safe here.
By the way, are you two hungry?
I've got some cake, so...
Ta-dah!
Whoa... Well, it still tastes the same, right?
Birthday?
Yeah. Today's my little girl's birthday.
She just turned four today.
Hina...
Yeah... Okay, here you go.
Thank you very much Mari.
It's great!
Even though it's a mess.
But it's round...
Birthday cakes should always be round.
It's like a rule, you know.
You're right.
What are we supposed to do now?
Good question... For now, let's get some sleep.
I have a feeling tomorrow's
going to be a busy day.
Communications have collapsed.
Massive casualties likely.