...and increasing damage from house collapses
and secondary disasters due to
the repeated aftershocks is feared.
Unless absolutely necessary...
Yuuki, do you need to throw up?
No.
What's wrong? Are you sick or something?
Then what?
Sis... I... Listen...
SIS, LISTEN...
What is it?
Listen...
What's the matter? Just tell me.
Listen... Just suppose...
If I... If I died... What would you do?
That's ridiculous! Don't say stupid things like that!
If you died... Dad and Mom would cry themselves to death.
So would I.
So, please, don't talk about dying anymore. OK?
Sorry...
Anyway, when we get home
let's tell Dad and Mom about
everything that happened to us, right?
I'll tell them how you were really strong the whole time.
Don't worry, I'll tell them how strong you were, too, sis!
You were cool!
And we have to give Mom her birthday present.
I'll tell her that you picked it out.
Well, sis. Not much farther,
and then we'll be home, won't we?
Uh-huh
listen, Yuuki.
Uh?
Summer break's only just started, you know?
Once things settle down a little bit
let's do nothing but have fun!
Last year I was so busy studying, I didn't have any fun.
I envied you then, because you didn't
have an exam that you had to go in and take.
But it was boring for you, too,
not having me take you anywhere, huh?
Uh-uh. I played with Itsuki.
Besides, sometimes you drew me pictures
of frogs, and I liked that, it was fun.
What? Those terrible pictures?
They weren't terrible!
Yes, they were!
They were cute!
You're so weird!
Yuuki, look! A horse!
It sure is.
Now, be gentle when you touch him.
Hey, Let's come back here together.
Uh-huh.
Yuuki, we're almost there!
Isn't that your friend's place, Yuuki?
Yeah... Kazu's house.
I hope our house is okay.
Mirai!
Hey!
Mayu!
Mirai! You're okay!
And you!
Thank goodness!
Mayu, what... Huh? Hey!
Cut it out! C'mon, Mayu, quit fooling around.
But, I couldn't get in touch with you at all!
I asked your mom, but she said there
wasn't any word on where either of you were!
Mayu! You were with my mom?!
Uh-huh...
I ran into her at the shelter at the elementary school.
She was so worried.
She got in touch with your dad
but she said you and your little
brother went off to Odaiba by yourselves.
And that she couldn't reach you at all!
I see... so Dad and Mom are all right.
Uh-huh.
She said your dad got hurt at his
office, but it's nothing serious.
Your mom's been going crazy, worrying about you two.
Thanks for telling me.
Is everyone at your home okay?
Yeah, they're fine.
Everyone's at home, but my mom's
in the last month of her pregnancy,
so we brought her here, just to be safe.
Thank goodness, they're all right.
Yeah...
Except I still haven't gotten in touch with Yuka.
I don't know what's happened to anyone else in our class.
I ran into Megu the day before yesterday,
but it looked like her mom had died.
What do you think What'll happen now, Mirai?
I wonder if school will start when it should.
By the way, where's your little brother?
Huh? He was right there a minute ago.
Oh...
Anyway, I'm glad you're both okay!
You should hurry up and get to the
elementary school and see your mom.
Uh.
Bye-bye!
Once things settle down, I'll come see how you're doing!
Why, you little...!
Come back here, you little brats!
Yuuki! I told you not to run off!
C'mon, Yuuki! Where are you running off to now?
To the school!
Yuuki!
I said wait!
Oh man.
Hey, Itsuki.
Oh! The Cell Phonian!
That's not my name. Didn't I tell you I'm Mirai, remember?
Mirai.
Yup. Hey, Itsuki?
Did you see Yuuki? I just saw him run through the gate.
Yuuki?! He's here?!
Yeah. We heard our mom was here.
Well, maybe he went over the the gym.
That's where your mom and everyone are taking shelter.
Is your family all right, Itsuki?
Yeah, but our house is wrecked.
Oh, Really?
Uh.
So, do you know where my mom is?
Over there!
Oh... Looks like she's out.
Mom?
Where's Yuuki's mom?
Why? Is something wrong?
She just left to get some fresh clothes from home.
I heard your dad is still in the hospital.
So he couldn't go himself.
The hospital?
Oh! But they say it's not serious!
It looks like he's okay.
Your mom really has been worried sick about you.
You should let see you're okay as soon as you can.
You still might be able to catch up. Go after her!
OK. I'll go home just as soon as I find Yuuki.
Thank you very much.
Yuuki!
Hmm... We can try the athletic field, next.
Has it grown a little?
I feel like I haven't seen it in ages.
Maybe if we wait here, Yuuki will come.
Yeah...
Yuuki...
Yuuki?
Yuuki!
Oh, that stupid...!
Huh? Wait for me!
I wanted to give Yuuki our marronnier journal.
Marronnier journal?
Yeah, it's an exchange journal.
It was Yuuki's turn to write in it.
You two were doing that?
Yeah.
Yuuki said we should both write in it when we started.
Yuuki?
Yuuki!
Darn it, Yuuki! Why did you just run off like that?!
I was looking for you!
Yeah... Sorry about that, Sis.
Yuuki?
Found him?
Yeah.
Yuuki, Itsuki was also...
What's the...
Did he go to the toilet?
That toilet's dirty. I mean it's really gross.
This is our classroom.
Here's my seat, and this one's Yuuki's.
They're so little!
Were the desks always this small and cute?
And look at all the doodles he made.
Oh, Yuuki...
Couldn't..
And over here, they hung the
pictures we drew on the bulletin board.
Look!
That's Yuuki's picture.
"In first grade, my family crossed the bridge to Odaiba."
"It was lots of fun. Yuuki Onozawa."
Yuuki...
Yuuki told me that he wanted to
go back to the bridge with everyone.
The reason I wanted to go to Odaiba...
was 'cuz I wanted us to see the bridge together.
What...? Why am I...?
Mirai?
It's strange... What's wrong with me?
Um... I'll go look for Yuuki!
Why? Why am I crying?
Yuuki...!
Why...?!
Sis, don't cry.
I'm here beside you.
Yuuki...
Darn it...
Next time you run off, I'm gonna get really mad!
Elementary school kids are good at calligraphy these days.
Can you tell which one's mine?
Let's see... Ah! Found it!
Got it!
It's good, huh?
It's too big.
But I can tell you put a lot of work into it.
I can tell. Because I'm your sister.
Yeah. I work hard because I love your name, Sis.
Yuuki wasn't in the toilet.
Yeah. Sorry. He's right here...
Huh? But, he was just here, sitting on this desk..
Oh... He never could keep still.
Always running around, all over...
Getting lost...
Um, sorry.
I'm... gonna go get our marronnier journal.
My house is right near here.
Wait. I'll go with you.
I'm going to go find my mom.
Okay, but...
I'm sorry.
I'm okay now. Let's go.
Itsuki! Get the journal some other time!
It's dangerous! Come out!
It's fine! I came here this morning, too!
Where's Yuuki?
Sis!
I'll go get Itsuki!
Yuuki, no! Come back!
Oh, you little...
Oh...!
Itsuki! That's enough. Come down.
Almost got it.
Found it!
Here you go.
Would you give it to Yuuki for me?
Uh-huh.
"July 20th. Planted the marronnier with Itsuki."
"Sis called the marronnier 'macaroni'."
"I think it's because she likes to eat."
What is this? He made that all up.
Thanks a lot, Itsuki. I'll
make sure he gets it right away.
Sure.
Yuuki.
Oh, where did you go?
You told me you were going to call Itsuki!
What were you doing? Come on, let's go home.
That means you too, Itsuki. You
have to get back to the shelter, right?
Um... Yeah.
Itsuki! Come on!
Yuuki!
Itsuki!
Itsuki, are you okay?
Yeah...
Yuuki, are you...
Sis... I...
Yuuki...
Tokyo Fire Department.
I'm sorry.
Yuuki...
Hey, sis, listen...
I...
Yuuki!
I died.
What message is left for family
lost in the Great Tokyo Earthquake?