So much smoke...
So... I guess this isn't a dream...
BURNING BRIDGE
Hi, sis. Where do you think that nice lady went?
I said I don't know.
Stop asking me about everything. Will you?
I told you, it'll be all right.
If worse comes to worst,
we'll go home on our own.
Oh, that's right. Maybe I can
get through on my phone.
No luck?
Not a bit.
I hope.. I hope Dad and Mom aren't hurt.
They're okay, right?
Right? Right, Sis? Do you think Dad and Mom are...
I don't know! I can't get through!
And I told you, don't ask me all these questions
OK?
Ah! Okay, you two. I'll bet you're hungry.
You get cranky when your
stomach's empty, huh?
Here. Breakfast.
Thanks a lot, Miss Mari.
Just call me Mari, Yuuki.
Oh! Rice balls!
You can eat some if you like, Mirai.
We've got drinks, too.
Why.. Why do you have these?
I remembered that some convenience stores give out
food during emergencies, so I went to check that out.
You weren't here when I woke up,
so I thought you'd left us here.
Oh-ho...
You got lonely because I wasn't here, didn't you?
You thought I'd run off.
Not really, it's just...
Okay then, let's make a promise.
A promise?
Uh-huh. From now on,
no more going off on our own.
No one leaves the group without
saying where they're going.
Uh-huh.
Why are you doing all this being nice to us?
Huh?
I mean, you have a kid waiting for you at home.
If you didn't stay with us,
you'd get back to her faster.
Yeah, that may be true,
but my home's in the same direction as yours,
and maybe that's some sort of fate.
So, let's go where we're going together.
Okay?
Uh!
Are you sure? We'll just slow you down you know..
Here. Eat this.
Hunger breeds pessimism.
You're just not happy when you are hungry.
Smile and attack the day!
Come on, let's eat!
Umejiso plum.
Thanks for giving the food!
What's you get?
I got salmon!
Man, isn't it hot!
Whew, boy...
Today's going to be a real summer scorcher.
I'll bet it's over 100.
You talk like an old man.
Oh? I get that a lot.
Mirai, you are way too direct!
C-Cut that out!
Give up?
Hi, sis, I'm thirsty.
Here.
Thanks a lot.
No problem. I'm glad I asked you to buy that yesterday.
Okay, let's see if there's been any news.
Since we'll drain the battery
if we watch for too long,
we'll have to take a peek and then shut it off.
Got it!
I'll now repeat the latest quake damage
report for the Tokyo metropolitan area.
All transportation services
have ceased operation,
with no restoration of service
seen in the near future.
Primary traffic restriction
rules are in effect,
and all traffic has been banned within the boundary of Tamagawa,
route 246, as well as the #7 loop road.
The confirmed death toll stands at 843,
but with countless others either
missing or gravely injured,
that number is expected to rise.
In addition, the sections of the city where
fires have started continue to...
Oh my god. So many people dead...
The fire department held
that anyone near these fire zones move to a shelter area as quickly as possible.
Currently, a large number of quake
victims are walking back to their homes.
We now turn to Prof. Noriaki Murata...
of the Keihan University Disaster Research
Center for more information.
Well, We are looking at upwards of six
and a half million people
trying to make their way home due to
this near-field earthquake in Tokyo.
Related to that, how long do you think
the aftershocks will continue?
We may possibly be seeing them
for the next three days
up to level 5 on the Shindo scale.
Those making their way home may...
I guess everyone's walking.
No telling when the trains will start
running again in this situation.
C'mon, Sis, let's go!
Let's try walking, too!
I feel a lot better now that I ate that rice ball!
But, we live it Setagaya. It's so far...
Doesn't seem like walking distance
at first thought.
Are you serious? Odaiba's cut off?
The bridge is on fire and the roads
are blocked all over the place.
This place'll sink!
We're in real trouble here.
It's okay. This land isn't in any danger of sinking.
OK?
But, I've heard that Odaiba's reclaimed land.
Hey! There's shade over here.
Daddy!
I'm worried. We don't have any food or water.
What are we going to do?
Relax. There are people who live around here.
Help will come soon.
You're right. Let's be glad that the
whole family's together, at least.
Let's!
I miss them...
Our Dad and Mom...
Shall we try to walk it?
You want to get back to your dad and
mom as soon as you can, right?
Uh-huh!
This is the Coast Guard!
We are transporting quake
victims via water bus.
Anyone wishing transport from
Odaiba to Hinode pier,
please assemble at the pier in Rainbow Park.
Those wishing transport to the Chiba side,
Okay! Looks like we take a boat to Hinode pier!
Darn it...
You okay?
I never should have worn these sandals.
They're giving me blisters.
Oh? Let me see.
Ooh, that looks painful.
Hang on.
One thing you always carry when you have a child.
Band-aids.
Hi, look at that. They got frogs on them!
Sis is a certified Frog Worlder!
Frog Worlder?
En..Enough! You don't have to tell her that stuff!
But thanks, I'm happy to use them.
Be my guest!
You're lucky!
Think you can walk now?
Yeah.
I see. Well, if it comes to worst,
I can carry you piggy-back. Rabbit!
Piggy-back!
Don't be stupid. I'm not a little kid.
Still, if you have any trouble, tell me.
Seriously, I would carry you.
I'm pretty sure my legs can handle it.
It's okay, I'll walk by myself...
Okay, that's the spirit!
Well, shall we go?
Your feet doing okay?
We are not in any big rush. Don't push yourself.
I've been wondering,
will we really get on the boat?
Look at all these people who want to get on, too.
Huh?
We won't get on?
Why don't we go and see first?
C'mon, I'm sure it'll be fine.
You're an optimist, aren't you, Mari?
Well, more like I'm positive.
Come on!
Uh-oh.
I'll help you.
Oh! Thank you so much!
Okay, ready, set... There we go!
Thank you. You saved me.
No problem.
And now your turn! Up you go!
Stick close to your mommy, okay?
Okay!
Really, thank you so much.
We're almost to the pier.
Right.
Mari's so nice, Isn't she?
More like she likes to butt in.
Sorry about that.
Yeah. Didn't you just promise that you
wouldn't leave the group without telling us first?
What happened over that?
Busted! I'm really sorry.
No, it's okay. You did a really good thing!
Everyone headed for Big Site,
keep moving straight!
Those boarding the boat for Hamamatsu-Chou,
make a left at the intersection up ahead, please!
Wow, this is getting really messy.
This is the only place to go for people who want to
go home before the train start again.
So we don't get split up.
Mirai, give me your hand, too.
I'll be fine. I told you, I'm not a little kid.
Then keep close. Don't get separated from us.
You got that?
Wait...
Mari!
Yuuki!
Yuuki...
Outta the way! Keep moving!
Yuuki? Mari?
Where are they?
Hey! Don't just stop here!
Mirai!
N-No!
Mari!
We are here, Sis!
Yuuki..
I think you'd better hold my hand.
Don't let go of my hands.
Again?!
It's okay.
That was like an explosion. Wasn't it
I can't believe the expressway collapsed.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Screw that! We'll never get across the bridge!
Damn it! That booms the only way.
Move it!
Not hurt?
Uh.
Can you walk?
Let's go!
This vessel is going to switch
over to sea rescue operations!
Please board the water bus immediately!
Do not board this vessel!
Hang on to my hand, no matter what.
Uh.
You too, Mirai.
Wait! That hurts!
Yuuki!
Mari!
Sis! Sis!
Yuuki!
Yuuki.
Sis!
SIS!
Sis...
Yuuki!
Sis!
The boat will be departing soon!
Please give priority to the weak and injured!
So many people... Maybe we should take the next
boat.
Let's just give it a try. Shall we?
Those who wish to board,
please wait for the next boat!
No luck.
You kids there! Get aboard, quick!
You too, Mom! Move it!
R-Right!
You okay?
Please wait for the next boat!
Calm down! Be careful!
This is awful.
Yeah. This isn't exactly an ideal situation.
Still, we got on the boat. Didn't we?
You've got a lot of nerve. Don't you?
The guy calls you "mom" and you're all like
"Right! Let's' go".
I guess I have gotten tougher
since my husband died.
It has't been easy for me since then.
Even though I'm alone,
I guess I just want to try to bring up Hina well.
Look... The bridge.
It's still on fire.
I see that looks like a tanker truck's burning.
What's...?
Uh-oh...
No way..
Mommy! People are falling!
If we'd been a little slower,
we'd have been on that one!
Look out! It's coming toward us!
If we'd been on that boat, then...
Mari?
You..
I'm sorry. For putting you in danger like that.
Thank you, Mari.
Tokyo Tower collapses! Desperate rescue efforts continue!