I hate it when they scold me.
And I hate being yelled at
in my spare time even more.
I've had it.
Everything could just fall apart, for all I care.
Day after day, that was what I thought...
As we have already reported, today at 3:45 PM,
a massive earthquake occurred,
centered in the Kanto region.
The quake's epicenter was in the northern area of
Tokyo Bay, at a depth of approximately 25 kilometers.
The scale of the earthquake
is estimated at magnitude 8.0.
Please beware of aftershocks and possible tsunamis.
ODAIBA SINKS
Onozawa? Mirai Onozawa?
Yes.
Okay, next. Kato?
Hiroko Kato.
Kubo? Mayumi Kubo.
Yes!
So, what are your grades?
I'm sunk. You, Mayu?
In the same boat.
Me, too. There's no way I can
show this to my parents.
They're so strict, I can guess my summer
vacation goodbye.
Lighten up, Yuka! There's no parent
who doesn't love their kids.
Have you met mine?
Wow, you're going to the Caribbean?
Yeah, they said they're taking it easy this year.
Where's your vacation house, Risa?
Canada. Daddy built a log house there.
Wow. Hey, why don't you come over tonight?
Mom's going to be baking us a soufflé.
Sure, I'll come.
Megu, you're so
lucky you live close to school.
So, where are you going for
summer vacation, Onozawa?
Oh, we don't have any plans like that.
I see. Well, you should go some place cool, then.
This year looks like it's gonna be a real scorcher.
Yeah...
Okay, as for your homework
over summer break
I was thinking I'd like a "future report,"
where you imagine yourself ten years from now.
Please, use your vacation time to
really think about that, okay?
Okay.
So, what are you gonna write about?
For my future report?
I have no idea.
You'll be a pianist, Yuka, so you're all set.
I like playing the piano,
but that's not an easy life.
Still, it may be nice, as long as
you're doing something you like.
I'll say.
But I don't even know what
I like or what I want to do.
Me, neither.
Hey, wanna head over to Shibuya?
Good idea!
Mirai, you come, too!
I can't. My parents are working today.
I have to watch the house.
Tomorrow's summer break.
Well, it's not like I'll be having much fun.
There's nothing I especially want to do.
I need to trim these bangs.
Getting annoying.
I don't really have any
special dreams for the future.
All I'm sure of is I don't wanna
grow up to be like THAT.
That won't be me in 10 years, will it?
Yuuki.
Like that, see? Oh!
Hi, there. Sis!
The Cell Phonian!
Wham'?!
I've never seen anyone from
planet Cell Phone before!
They anger easily.
What have you been telling him?!
Onozawa. So, how's middle school?
Nothing special.
It has to be better than that.
But it really is nothing special.
What are you guys doing after school?
Oh, it's a favor for Yuuki.
The marronnier tree dad got me
won't grow big at home, so I brought it to school.
Teacher said I could plant it over there.
I know! Sis, you help, too!
Huh?!
Good idea.
Isn't it?
No way.
Oh, I'm dripping wet!
It's good to work up a sweat once in a while.
Says who.
Now it'll grow big.
Yeah. Thanks, Itsuki.
Let's come and water it during summer break.
Right!
Let's go home, Yuuki.
Yeah!
You said we play soccer after this was planted.
Oh, that's right.
Oh my god.
What is with him?
Mirai?
Oh? You're home.
Say "I'm home" when you walk in!
I thought you were a burglar.
I'm heading out. I've got clients waiting.
There's cake here.
Hyping it up, much?
I have to get going.
Share that cake with Yuuki, okay?
Aren't you having any?
Mommy's on a diet, dear.
They're wedges!
You should have gotten a round one!
Oh, and you'd better bring in the laundry,
won't you, Mirai?
It looks like rain.
What's?
Wash your plates after you have your cake.
Then wait for an express package
and groceries from the co-op.
Get the produce in the fridge
as soon as it comes, okay?
Okay, I'll be back sometime around 7:00.
See you later!
And leave your report card out. I'll look at it later.
Like I care, after all that
stuff you told me to do.
What's that?
For Mom. For her birthday.
"To Mom, Happy Birthday."
Bor-ing.
Boring?
No, I guess it's okay.
What are you giving her, Sis?
Nothing special.
Well, why don't we both give this to her?
You drew it! YOU give it to her!
There's cake. Want some?
It's good, huh?
Bor-ing.
Would it be better if we
could eat with mom, right?
But Mommy has to go out!
Share that cake with Yuuki. Mommy's on a diet!
You sound just like her! Do it again!
What's wrong?
You're still such a little kid, Yuuki.
Darn it... I wanted to eat a round cake.
How can you not know that birthday
cake is supposed to be round?
Sis! This is awesome!
Wait. I'm super busy right now.
The Cell Phonian appears...
I'm home.
Ah, it's cool in here.
Welcome home.
Hm? Where's your mom?
Not home yet.
Oh. Well, I'll take a shower, then.
Did you remember? Today's Mom's birthday.
Yeah, so it is.
Ah... That feels better.
Hey, hey!
Don't leave things lying around, put those away.
So... Summer break starts tomorrow.
Yeah. You should get your homework
done as soon as you can.
That's not what I meant.
Aren't we going somewhere on vacation?
Everyone's always "Exams! Exams!",
we never go anywhere.
Well, that's true...
Why don't we ask your mom about that?
No way. She gets mad over nothing all the time.
Because she's busy with work now.
Well, maybe she's due for a vacation.
I'm home.
Hi, Mom!
Hello.
Arg! I forgot to buy milk.
Hi, Dear. What about dinner?
Heating it up right now.
It's after 8 o'clock.
It's not like I can help it! I work too, you know!
No, it's just... but the kids are hungry.
So? I said I'm making it now!
Oh, would you cut that out!
Dad, don't blame it on us!
What're you looking so down about?
I didn't give her my present.
Why are you always so worried about them.
Even though you're just a kid...
So are you, you know, sis.
Don't you want Mom and Dad to get along?
That would be nice.
At this point, they can do
what they want, for all I care.
What are you up to?
Nothing!
Parents got a look at my future report.
Got surprise lecture about how
I had to go to college first.
Same here. Got lectured about
not missing piano lessons.
Sucks.
So, what is this I wanna be?
My name may mean "future",
but I have no idea what mine is.
So hot...
Whoops! Morning.
See you.
Bye.
Please, Mom?!
You-Chan, don't be selfish.
I have work to do. It can't be helped.
So, why can't Sis and I go by ourselves?
By yourselves?
Uh, What?
Huh?! A robot exhibit?!
They're holding it over at Odaiba.
Do me a favor and take him, OK?
I don't wanna go see some stupid robots!
Besides, why do I have to
play nursemaid for Yuuki?
I...
What's the big deal? You're on summer break.
You said you wouldn't give up your
precious time for summer classes,
so I know you're free!
Alright, Fine!
You want me to take him? I'll take him!
Sis! Look at the bridge!
We came here once before! Look!
All right! OK, Jesus!
Now arriving at Daiba. Daiba.
Oh! Odaiba! We have to get off.
Huh? Oh...
Sis, let's take the bus.
We got off too soon because you
kept going on about Odaiba.
Deal with it!
It's hot.
No, it isn't!
Sure is hot.
Let's go.
This? This is what you wanted to see?
You don't?
OK, fine.
Come on, let's go.
Sis, you look! You can pet them!
Aw... It's so cute.
Kitty! Paw! Give me your paw!
Hey, they've got ones you can operate over there!
These are quadruped robots,
designed to move by crawling.
Their four legs can adjust to uneven terrain,
allowing their operation on the
rough ground of a disaster area.
Its mobility can be used by rescue
teams in their operations
and its radar system can find buried survivors.
It's awesome! Sis, you give it a try!
Its on board
electromagnetic search radar
can detect the respiration of an immobilized
person from 5 meters away.
The range can be extended to 8 meters
if they can move even a little bit.
Look at it go!
Hi, sis,
Don't be so rough with it.
It was fine!
Hey, are you going to be there all day?
Could you hurry up?
Thanks a lot.
C'mon, Sis, why don't we
go buy Mom a present for her birthday?
Huh? Never mind about that.
For starters, if she'd just brought you herself,
then I wouldn't have had such a rotten day.
She looks down on me because
she thinks I'm a kid.
But...
For another thing, I don't have any money.
I do! I have some.
Which one should we get, Sis?
Hey, how about that one?
That's a popular one.
Oh, you don't say.
It's nice to get something
like this once in a while.
Oh, I'm sorry. Did you want this?
No...
Sorry,
Here, take it. It's too flashy
for my grandma, anyway.
That's okay.
Take it, I insist.
Really, it's okay.
How about this one, Sis?
This one's nice, too!
Getting somebody a present?
Yeah.
It's our mom's birthday.
Oh, that's sweet.
I'd definitely cry if my
daughter gave me this as a gift.
Thanks a lot!
Hope your mom likes it.
There's a lot of people today.
Be careful you don't get lost.
Bye!
Don't treat me like a kid.
C'mon, Sis, let's get this one. Mom likes flowers!
Buy what you want.
Sis, I gotta go to the toilet.
So, go.
Here, hold this for me.
Oh, after you're done, buy us a drink.
I'll be outside.
Sure!
So hot...
Hey! You mind not stopping in the entrance?
Oh, I've had it!
Why is everything trying so hard to piss me off?
Day after day, everything makes me angry.
Seriously.
What's with that face?
I wonder..
Is anything good going to happen in my life?
I've had it. It's all such a pain.
The whole world can fall apart, for all I care.
Earthquake?
No way... Ah!
Yuuki.
YUUKI!
Magnitude 8.0. Tokyo has been destroyed.