Zero-Four, reaction.
Zero-Two, confirming 2-5-2.
It's dangerous. Please step back.
We are currently using our Robo-Qs and other search
equipment in an all-out effort to locate survivors.
We've already confirmed one survivor.
How long until they can be rescued?
He's buried under multiple sections of reinforced concrete
over 20 cm thick, but it should be any moment now.
We have Team 1 assisting with the rescue.
SUMMER SUNSET
Okay, we'll do our best and all get home, okay?
Mari, are you okay now?
Uh-huh! I'm all better now, thanks to you two.
See for yourselves!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
What I tell you?
Jeez...
Now we'll cut through Roppongi and come out in Shibuya.
Right.
I used to pass by here coming
home from school all the time
but it's like a different city now.
Huh? What's that?
Go in once that rebar on top's been pulled off!
Robots..
Okay! Don't skimp on the safety checks!
Okay! Go in from number 2!
Two-five-two, survivor in need
of aid, sighted! He's conscious!
You okay?
Speak to us! You okay?
You all right? Can you tell us your name?
You're drawing robots!
You draw them really good!
You like robots?
Yeah! And I draw them all the time!
Do you like drawing pictures, too?
Well, not pictures, so much.
I like robots.
I'm taking down lots of notes so I can look them up later.
Hey, you know about those?
It's the first time they're being used in the field.
I saw those at the exhibit!
You, too?
Well, do you know what that one is?
Uh-uh.
Yuuki?
Over there, see?
They trace the arm movements from the control unit.
Each arm can lift one ton.
You know a lot about them, huh?
Yeah.
Someday, I want to build robots
just like the ones over there.
What's it doing? Showing off? Since the job is done.
You don't know anything, do you?
It's double-checking to see if there
are any other people who need help here.
It fell over!
Well, it's light weight robot, so
the balance is bad when it walks!
That robot's called a semi-autonomous type.
After you enter the coordinates, it moves on its own.
Well, I've gotta get going now.
Thanks a lot, big brother.
My name's Kento. Kento Nonomiya.
My name's Yuuki Onozawa. I'm in the third grade!
Oh? I'm in the seventh grade.
Seventh grade? Just like my big sister!
I hope I'll see you again.
Sure. See you!
That's the type they call an otaku.
A robotaku.
This earthquake is being called the greatest urban
near-field earthquake ever observed in this nation.
According to the government crisis management
center, the death toll is estimated at 180,000
even higher than the 140,000 killed
in the Great Kanto earthquake of 1923.
While the fires around the quake's epicenter are being
extinguished, according to Tokyo Fire Department reports,
150,000 victims may still be threatened,
with 200,000 injured, although that number is...
No word on Sancha, huh?
Mari...
Mm. I'm okay. Thank you.
What? What's wrong?
A rat!
A rat?
Oh. The store...
Yeah. There are lots of rats in this city, so...
What?
Yuuki?!
What's wrong?
I'm OK.
My head was just hurting a little, that's all.
Ow! Your head is burning up!
Maybe it's heatstroke.
Wait in the shade. I'll go see
if there's any medicine I can get.
OK.
Look, tell us if you feel sick, okay?
It'll be a lot of trouble if you start fainting on us.
Sorry.
Jeez...
Oh! It's Kento!
What? Hey! Keep still!
I'm afraid This is all the
municipal services people gave me.
Thanks, it's a real help.
Yuuki!
Mirai? Wait! What are you doing? Where are you going?
Sorry! I'll be right back!
Oh...!
Kento!
Yuuki.
Yuuki! We three promised to stick together, right?
Robotaku.
Sis, we saw those frogbots at the Miraikan, remember?
Frogbots? Yeah, they do look like frogs, don't they?
They're waterproof to 20 atmospheres.
Waterproof to 20 atmospheres?
Right. They can withstand the pressure
up to 200 meters below the surface.
The question is whether that's necessary or not.
Wow...
Definitely otaku.
Otaku?
I mean... You know all this stuff about robots.
Um. Cause I like them.
If it weren't for robots, my family might have died.
That was back when I was in elementary school.
I can see the survivors.
Okay, don't use the scope. Proceed carefully.
1 and 2, I need a power cutter and a
spreader right now to get the door open!
Roger!
If that robot hadn't been there,
I don't think they could have saved my whole family.
That's why I want to design
rescue robots like that, some day.
To help someone else.
I'm sorry I called you an otaku before.
That's okay. After all, I do like robots a lot.
Until that robot saved them,
I always thought my parents
and my big sister were annoying.
But, that night, I was really
praying that I wouldn't lose them.
Do you two live around here?
Uh-uh. We live near Kinuta Park.
I see. Well, I hope you get home, soon.
Uh.
Oh, yeah.
For you, Yuuki.
I can have it?!
Sure. I've already memorized it.
Thank you!
How are we going to explain this to Mari?
God! I was really worried about you!
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
He's fine. You saw how he was running before.
I'm fine.
Yuuki? Are you okay?
Why don't we rest for a while?
A frog baseball team...
What are you talking about, Yuuki?
It really is!
It's raining.
Yeah.
I really appreciate it.
No trouble at all. See you in a bit.
He said he'd be back in 20 or 30 minutes.
Let's rest a little till then. Why don't we?
Found another one?
Yeah.
This place is full of frogs, huh?
Uh.
Maybe the owner really likes frogs, like you do.
Sis...
You're finished?
Don't want it.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
Maybe he caught a cold from sleeping outside.
Oh, no sis!
Yuuki!
Are you okay?!
I'm... I'm fine...
I just ate too much.
Get some sleep, okay?
It's okay. It's okay.
Earthquake?
We're okay. It was just a little one.
Looks like Mari, even slept right through it.
I was dreaming about the robot exhibit.
You really like robots, don't you?
But I think Kento's even more amazing.
'Cuz he's a robotaku?
He is a robot expert.
Kento's the same age as me,
but it's so great that he knows just what he wants to do.
Know what?
Up till now, all I've done is complain about Dad and Mom.
You know,
But they've actually done all
sorts of things for us, haven't they?
All I ever thought about... were the bad things...
And now...
I realize how much I don't want them to die.
When we get home... Let's be a little nicer to them, okay?
Yeah... I hope we can all be nice to each other.
Yeah.
Let's throw Mom another birthday party.
It'll be a surprise party. And we'll buy her a round cake.
Yeah.
Hey, Sis?
The reason I wanted to go to Odaiba...
was 'cuz I wanted us to see the bridge together.
Yeah. You told me that back in Shiba Park.
I did?
Well, we were arguing, so...
Next time, let's all of us go back to Odaiba.
Sure thing. Except the bridge is gone, now.
They'll build a new one.
Yuuki?
That's my Frogbot 1!
Hey! Wait! Where are you going?
Just to watch the robots!
Uh?
I touched it!
Hey, kid! Don't bother it, okay?
Yuuki, let's go back to Mari.
Right.
What?
Yuuki, did you really see Kento there?
Uh.
See? There's nobody here. We can't go in, anyway.
Let's go back, Yuuki.
Emm.
Sis! Up there! Look!
What is he doing up here?!
Kento!
What are you doing?! That's dangerous!
The robot's leg is caught in
some debris! Keep away from here!
Huh?!
You're the one who needs to get away from there!
Agh! What's he doing now?!
Yuuki! Go get Mari!
Uh!
Oh...!
Kento!
Stay back! Get an adult!
I already called for one, you dope!
Kento, reach out your hand!
Take this!
Let it go!
Just leave it already!
Thanks! You're pretty strong, aren't you?
Okay, I'll get up top and pull you up.
Here!
Close one, huh?
That was a little more than
close! Whose fault was this any...
You're hurt?!
Are you in danger? Don't move! We'll be right up there!
Concentrate the search on the area
where the scanner signal was strongest!
We use these robots to avoid secondary disasters.
Which is rendered pointless if
you go and get yourselves hurt!
You're both old enough to know better!
Now don't pull a damn fool stunt like this again!
Yes, sir.
Personnel or equipment, any problems?
No, sir!
Okay, next one!
Captain..
Mirai...
I'm sorry for putting you in danger like that.
And... For saving me... Thank you.
That's okay. It was nothing...
'Cuz Sis is brave, huh?
There was nothing brave about this, for heaven's sake!
What did you plan to do if things went wrong?!
I'm sorry.
Kento, please tell me more about robots next time.
Uh.
I'll see you again, I promise.
Okay, shall we go?
Uh!
What?
I was thinking how cool you were, Sis!
Next time there's a robot exhibition
in Tokyo, let's all go together!
Dad and Mom and you.
And Kento, too!
Uh.
Mirai! Hey, Yuuki!
Shall we go?
Uh!
Yuuki!
Yuuki! Yuuki!
What's wrong?! Answer me! Yuuki!
Yuuki!
Number of injured now exceeds the
Great Kanto Earthquake, still climbing.