Zero-One, status report.
We've rendezvoused with the fire
department. Initiating rescue operations.
Relief supplies are being distributed in Shiba Park
by the city of Tokyo and Minato ward.
Please follow the directions to Shiba Park.
If you are injured, please remain here.
To repeat, relief supplies are
being distributed in Shiba Park...
Have they arrived?
No, next boat. It should be arriving in about 5 minutes.
Shiba Park is about 15 minutes away...
Mirai, are all your blisters all right?
Yeah.
Okay then, shall we get going?
Right.
Yesterday, at approximately 3:46 PM, a major
earthquake occurred, centered on the Kanto region.
The epicenter was in northern Tokyo
Bay, at a depth of 25 kilometers.
The strength of the quake is estimated at magnitude 8.0.
Ugh... Uh-oh.
A PROMISE BY THE THREE
Sis! I can see Tokyo Tower!
We're close to home now, right?
I said we're not.
But we can see Tokyo Tower from home.
Even so, home's still far away!
Mirai, are you okay?
I... I'm fine.
Um... I'll be able to wash up at
the park when we get there, won't I?
Hm...
They'll have toilets, but I
don't know if the water's running.
Did you get dirty somewhere?
Um... No.
Oh, yeah. Sis, when we get
home, I'll let you have my pudding.
Why would you bring that up now?
'Cuz you're trying so hard!
Look, I'm not some little kid who needs snack time!
Liar! You're like Sergeant Snack Time!
"Sergeant Snack Time"?
Yeah!
Ugh... I might be in trouble here...
Mirai, do you have a stomachache?
I'm fine.
Didn't I say to tell me when you're hurting?
Hold on.
gonna check things
Are you hungry, sis?
When we get home, let's go to grandpa's place in Hokkaido.
We can get soft-serve or even...
We're not going to Hokkaido this year!
Dad told me...
Hey! Sorry I took so long!
Sorry, Mirai.
Did that cake upset your stomach?
Um, no. It didn't.
Here.
Portable toilet.
What?! This is a toilet?! Let me see!
Whoa, it's made out of paper!
Check this out!
Just say when you need it. You can use it anywhere.
Um... I'm good for now.
Oh?
Portable toilets and wet wipes here!
So many people...
Yeah.
Toilets... Where're the toilets?
Ah! We might be able to get food over there.
Relief supplies are being
distributed! One per person, please!
Ramen!
Looks like they're giving it out over there.
Sis, they've got instant ramen!
Hey, Mirai...
That was kind of a big one just now, huh?
Let's go some place and catch our breath for now.
What are those? Tents?
No, they look like toilets.
I'm going over there...
We'll wait under these trees over here.
For heaven's sake... She's stubborn. I'll give her that.
Hey! This spot's open!
Oh, we're saved!
Lucky!
Talk about your super-good timing!
Right.
Hey!
No cutting! Wait your turn!
What? The spot was open.
You saw there was a line behind you! Don't lie to me!
Hey, he cut in front of you, too. Say something!
Huh?!
Hey! Don't hide behind that kid!
Aren't you ashamed to be doing that in front of children?
How old are you, anyway?!
How the hell old are you, pal?!
Don't play that game with me! We're about the same!
Lemme go! You gonna follow the rules or not?!
Shut up, you son of a bitch!
Can't get through?
I hope you can get through to Hina, soon, Mari.
Yeah... By the way, you think
Sergeant Snack Time is all right?
Huh?
What's wrong?
M-Mari...
Chocolate and M.R.E.s, here!
They're all mixed together.
I'll take some ramen!
Sorry, but this tent is out of instant ramen!
That guy had two.
Yeah. Some grownups are like that.
Even while they tell kids how to act.
I'm sure he has a reason. Maybe
he's taking it to someone who's hurt.
A reason. Right...
Ow!
Mirai!
Are you okay?! Did you get burned?
The nerve! She didn't even apologize!
Here.
Mirai dear.
Here you go.
Sis, do you want me to hold it?
No way! I said I was fine, didn't I?!
I heard they brought in people from Shinagawa!
Ow!
Sorry!
Pardon me!
Sis!
Mirai! You okay?
What's the deal?!
What's that?
I think around here is where they're
bringing the people who have died.
Um, excuse me.
Yes?
Any word on how Sancha is doing?
Sancha, huh? Any word from Sancha?
Sorry, we don't have any reports in from there yet.
When will I get a call through?
I wonder if the tree we planted is doing okay.
Who cares about that?!
Stupid
I wonder if Dad and Mom are okay...
I told you, I don't know!
Even you should be able to understand that!
Mirai! Yuuki!
Looks like our route home is pretty much okay.
Really?!
Really!
This is Shiba Park, where we are now.
And, over here, is Shibuya.
If we follow this straight,
we'll get to my home in Sangenjaya.
After that, we follow Setagaya Street,
then cut over here to Kinuta Park.
From there, it's just a short hop to your home.
So, for now, why don't you come with me to Sangenjaya?
And then it's a short hop to our house!
Let's hit the road!
Uh!
And you'll give it your best too, right, Mirai?
Maybe your phone will get
through when we get to the school.
That makes no sense.
I'm sure Yuuki just means he hopes
you'll get through. Isn't that right?
Because you think then she'll be happy too, right?
Okay, then!
All right, once I get back from
dumping our trash, we'll set out.
It's like you and Mari are on the same wavelength.
Is your stomach okay?
I think so.
Once we get back home, you can
have more than just my pudding.
Oh, for... Could you stop just talking about food, huh?
Is your stomach still hurting, sis?
Not really.
Then what? We're almost home.
I told you, we're NOT almost home! Besides...
We don't even know if our house will
still be standing when we get there!
Not to mention... I keep calling Mom
and Dad, but I can't even get through.
Well, maybe the cell phone's still...
Or maybe they just don't care
whether we're all right or not!
I really can't take it anymore...
Here.
Oh, God, I'm so sick of how you do that!
If you have something to say, then say it!
Stop copying other people!
First of all, if you hadn't wanted to see that
robot exhibit, we wouldn't even be in this mess!
This is all your fault!
I wanted to see it...
I wanted to see the bridge...
Because they said they weren't going
to take us anywhere for summer vacation.
So, I thought you and me could
go see the bridge together...!
That wasn't all..
How far did he go?
Oh, there you are!
You two weren't where I left you,
so I've been looking everywhere!
I'm sorry.
Did something happen? Where's Yuuki?
I.. Hang on, I'll go look for him!
Wait! Mirai?
I'll be right back!
That was a big one, huh?
Did another building fall down?
Stop that. You're scaring me.
Yuuki!
Yuuki! Yuuki, come on!
Jeez... Mari's back. Come on. Let's go now.
You don't understand, Sis.
You can see our house from Tokyo Tower.
I know! But we know the way to get home now.
So let's go back.
We know the way back, but not if our house is okay!
Even I can understand that much!
And that's why I want to see how it is now!
If you see it's okay, then you can calm down, right, Sis?
I know I'll see our house.
'Cuz we can see Tokyo Tower from home...
So, I know I'll...
Sis, Mom and Dad aren't dead..
I miss Dad and Mom!
Hi kids,what's the matter?
What's the matter?
Well, looks like they're lost.
Miss, are you two by yourselves?
Where's your father? Or your mother?
Oh, I'm sorry! I didn't mean to make you cry
It's all right. We just haven't been able to get in touch.
We'll see you.
Let's get home soon and give Mom her present, okay?
No way... Yuuki!
Yuuki!
Sis!
Yuuki?
You...ki?
Hey! C'mon, don't kid around, OK?
You can't be..
No...
I'm fine.
Ow!
Check the injured! Bring the car around
Injured! Get the shamble apart
Those who can move, help them
Aside from that lump, are you okay, Yuuki?
Yeah.
Honestly, you two. I was really worried!
I'm sorry.
Good, glad the attitude's gone.
So, that promise we made in
Odaiba. From now on, we keep it, okay?
Okay.
Good, then now we'll head to a
shelter area at a middle school.
Grab all our bags, won't you?
Right! Huh? Right now?
We have to try to get there before sundown.
Don't forget our promise.
The three of us are going home together!
Okay!
At a school shelter area in Minato
ward. Victims there await relief.