Someone said that noise before
was Tokyo Tower coming down!
Seriously?!
What's wrong?
Tokyo tower really did fall, didn't it?
SCHOOLHOUSE OF LAMENTATION
I could see it from my classroom..
Tokyo Tower...
Is that around here? Just what's
the school it is you go to, Mirai?
It's Rikka Girls' Academy.
Really?!
That's where the shelter area we're headed for is.
What? No way! Really?
I'm impressed, Mirai. That's a prestigious school.
No... I barely passed getting in.
I heard it was renovated just recently.
One of the municipal workers told me
that was why the buildings in
this area have so little damage.
Yeah, the building construction is
new, but it's designed to looks old.
Mom liked that about it, too.
Mom also said it was the school she wanted to go to.
That's why she was so happy when
sis was accepted that mom fell down.
She fell down?
Uh-huh!
That was at the school's entrance ceremony.
Wha...?! Mom!
Oh...! Stop tripping over nothing! You're embarrassing us!
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh, no. Now what do I do?
It was her fault for wearing such high heels.
That scrape looked like it really hurt.
I don't care, but... She was
in such a bad mood after that.
You know, she was probably just angry with herself.
Doing something like that at
her daughter's entrance ceremony.
If it had been me, I probably would have cried.
You're like her, aren't you?
What?! I'm not like her! At all!
No, you totally are!
I'm totally not!
"Mommy has to go out!"
Keep away from the school building, please!
Somehow, it doesn't seem like my school.
Is there anyone who hasn't gotten water yet?
Anyone who hasn't gotten water?
You must be thirsty. Have some water.
Oh. Thank you.
Have you been to the hospital yet?
Yes. I went, but it's so crowded
that there was no one to see him.
There's lots of people here who are hurt, huh?
There are a lot of hospitals located
in this part of the city, Yuuki.
Looks like they're all full up, though.
It's hard to believe.
That you go to school here, Mirai.
Yeah, but...
I feel like we've come to some
place I've never seen before.
That's not surprising.
Still, we feel a lot better with you
here, since you know the place so well.
Isn't that right?
Besides, I always kind of wanted
to come to see your school, Sis.
But it's a girls' school, so I
figured they wouldn't let me in.
You could come visit during the culture fair.
Not like I'd invite you...
Oh, yeah! Yuuki!
Come on, I'm gonna show you something cool.
This way!
Hey, Sis. What's in here?
Stained glass windows. Will you see? They're SO pretty!
Look! Over there!
Mom...?
Megu...
Soufflés...
Megu mentioned it once.
That.. That her mom made her soufflés...
It's not like Megu and I were really close or anything.
I.. I kind of disliked her, actually, but...
But I hated...
Seeing her that sad... I just hated it.
I couldn't do anything to help her.
What can any of us do?
In the end, about this.
It's been one day since the quake,
but we've yet to receive detailed
damage reports from all areas.
However, according to the Tokyo Fire Department,
we've gotten word that 200,000
homes have been lost to fires,
Doesn't seem much cooler, even though it's nighttime now.
Yeah, you're right.
But I have a secret..
I know of a place.
A place that's a tiny bit cooler.
This place is a little bit cooler, thanks to the water.
I can imagine you've been through a lot,
but please, at least get some rest tonight.
Pardon me, but, who are you?
My name's Furuichi, and as you
can see, I'm just an old man.
I can't do very much to help, but at the very least
I can lead you some place a little cooler.
They looked like this.
The stained glass windows I wanted to show you, Yuuki.
They sparkled like this. So pretty...
It may not be a birthday cake,
but I like the moon when it's round.
Like a big, tasty pancake.
I like crescent moons. I like the name.
Oh! Say, did you know this?
Some people call the crescent moon a "paper moon".
Oh? Why?
Don't know.
Nothing!
That light...
It must be Mr. Furuichi. He's
leading someone else over here.
Aftershock.
Keep calm, please! If you're near a window, move back!
There has just been another major aftershock.
Beware of fires, crumbling
buildings, and any falling objects.
God, how long is this gonna go on?
It's just annoying now.
Was anyone injured?
The window glass is cracked! Please,
keep away from the school building!
I can't take this anymore!
We're okay! It's safe now!
Big one, huh?
Yeah.
You two are so great. You're really holding up.
No matter what, we keep our promise to each other.
We won't get separated, okay?
Is there anybody here whose hurt?
It's seems Mr. Furuichi must be a local volunteer.
We need to thank him.
Ah, so here you are.
Thank you so much for taking care of the children.
Oh... It's nothing.
You're not hurt?
Uh..no, ma'am.
It must have been frightening, but we're safe now.
Your daddy and mommy will come for you soon.
I know. Why don't I give you some candy?
Grandma bought it for you. I know how much you like sweets.
Here.
Th-Thank you very much.
Here you go.
Thank you!
You like those candies, don't you?
Misako!
Hello, Dear.
I want you to stay in the auditorium. It's safe in there.
She's your wife?
She wasn't bothering you, was she?
No, not at all.
She gave me some yummy candy!
Well, good for you. Enjoy it, please. Shall we go, Dear?
But Dear, the children...
It's all right. They'll be safe here.
Come along.
That old lady, she..
Another one!
Stay close.
No! No!
It's okay! It won't reach us here.
Chii! Koh!
I'm coming!
Misako!
Dear...
You don't have to go.
But what about the children...!
That's enough.
Chii!
Misako. Stop this, now.
Mr. Furuichi!
Oh, thank you. Are you all right?
Yes. Are you hurt?
We're fine. Now, come along, Misako.
Hey... That old lady keeps calling us Chii and Koh.
I wonder why?
Uh..
Maybe... I think she's mistaken the
two of you for her own grandchildren.
Mr. Furuichi's grandchildren
were killed in the quake yesterday.
They apparently came for a
surprise visit from the country...
Chii... Koh...
It must be so hard for him
but he's been all over, helping out here and there.
He's an inspiration.
If you need water or blankets, please come
on over to the tents on the athletic field.
We've been gathering them from here and there.
Thank you very much.
Oh, yes!
Have you had any thing to eat yet?
We'll be having curry udon on the athletic field, soon.
Ah!
Despite all the terrible things that
happened to everyone in this quake...
I'm thankful. I truly am.
What's wrong? Can't move?
Not a bit.
Me, neither. There's something...
You must be thirsty. How about some water?
Thank you. I'd love some, Mr. Furuichi.
You really are a life saver. Despite
all that's happened to everyone...
No, no. This is all that I can do.
What's wrong?
But, mister...
After what happened to you grand-kid..
You heard, then?
Yes..
They were my daughter's kids, from Okayama.
I hear they barely got any
tremors in that part of the country.
I'd just asked them to come visit.
That's the most tragic part of it.
They were actually just little
older than you and your brother now.
But to my wife, they'll always be little kids.
I'm glad you're all okay.
That's really good.
It should have been me who died.
I'd rather the young ones who live.
He's amazing. Mr. Furuichi...
Makes me think I wasn't able to do anything for Megu.
Come here.
There are things to do at times like these, right..
Uh-huh.
Communications still out. Families concerned for members.