[WOMEN A grunts]
[WOMEN A screams]
♪
[NARRATOR] Sapporo, a city
that was specifically designed
to serve as the center of the
Hokkaido settlement effort.
At the time, it wasn't
as populated as Otaru.
But it flourished due to the
munitions industry's success
in the war.
[SHIRAISHI]
Hey, mister.
Where can we find a
room around here?
We've been traveling,
and we're exhausted.
I do know of an
old hotel nearby.
A young woman took it
over just recently,
and let me tell you, buddy.
She's a total knockout!
Yeah, that sounds perfect.
[SHOPKEEPER] It's called
the Sapporo World Hotel.
[IENAGA] Good day. I am Ienaga.
The proprietress here.
Welcome, sir.
[IENAGA]
What is he doing here?
Well, look at that.
You're a pretty one.
Allow me to show
you to your room.
So, are you here in
Sapporo as a tourist?
[USHIYAMA] Something like that.
I heard that you're a widow.
[IENAGA]
That's right.
My husband left this hotel
to me when he passed away.
What about before that?
I heard an old couple
ran it until recently.
Yes, my husband's parents.
[IENAGA] Does he know
who I am? Or not?
[USHIYAMA]
Hey, Miss.
You've got a nice ass,
but your voice also sounds
like a sweet little bird.
I want it in my ear all night.
You're too kind, sir.
Have you already eaten?
If you're up for
something adventurous,
there's a Chinese
place near here.
They have a very unique way of
thinking and seeing the world.
[IENAGA] They say that if you
wish to heal a part of the body
that's afflicted, you should
eat that same part of an animal.
If your eyes have gone bad,
then, eat some eyes.
If you have a sick heart,
then eat a heart.
There was an old guy in Abashiri
who said the same exact thing.
What're you, a doctor?
Are you trying to say
that it actually works?
Yes, as a matter of fact,
it works beautifully.
Well, well. Then I wonder
if you could help me.
What should I take for
more stamina? In bed.
Oh, but surely you're not
in need of that, sir.
Beautiful thing.
Let me have you.
So much strength
in those arms.
All the power of a wild beast.
I find them very attractive.
[SUGIMOTO]
Excuse me!
Is there anybody here?
I have some new guests
that require my attention.
Please excuse me.
[snorts]
I'll be waiting.
Welcome new guests.
I'm the proprietress, Ienaga.
[SHIRAISHI] Yoshitake Shiraishi.
And I'm single. No girlfriend.
Also a loyal and
passionate companion.
[IENAGA]
Great. Another one.
[SUGIMOTO]
This place is like a maze.
[IENAGA]
It's a very old hotel,
so it's been remodeled many
times over the years.
[SHIRAISHI] Miss Ienaga,
what's your first name?
[IENAGA]
It's Kano, sir.
Beautiful, like you.
This place just feels weird.
You're used to sleeping
on pine leaves.
This was bound to feel strange.
Whoa! This girl has
set me on fire.
That means nothing.
The question is,
how is she in bed?
You need one with more
meat on her bones.
No, it's too late! I think
I'm in love with her!
I'm gonna do my best to
talk her into the sack.
[IENAGA] So, Shiraishi doesn't
know who I am, either.
I guess their both being
here is just a coincidence.
[IENAGA]
No matter.
For now, I want Ushiyama's
strong body for myself.
It'll get me one step closer
to the perfect human.
[IENAGA]
I'll do the usual:
get him liquored up, then use
the gas to put him to sleep.
[SHIRAISHI]
Huh? There you are!
I've been looking
all over for you!
I'm sorry, I'm a little busy.
We can talk later, okay?
[SHIRAISHI]
Why don't I help you?
Eh? Huh?
[SHIRAISHI]
How did she...?
Miss Ienaga, please, wait!
[SHIRAISHI]
Maybe this room.
[SHIRAISHI grunts]
[groans]
[SHIRAISHI]
Kano, are you...?
Huh, I thought for sure
you must've come in here.
[SHIRAISHI]
Maybe she just left?
Did I just imagine the
proprietress was here?
Come to me soon, woman.
I don't like to wait.
[IENAGA]
Oh no! He'll find Shiraishi!
Shiraishi, behind you!
[IENAGA]
Forget it, I'll just kill him.
[yelps]
Did you just hear
a weird noise?
That was my stomach.
[stomache growls]
[yells]
[SHIRAISHI yells, grunts]
What kind of trap is this?
I can't see a thing.
[SHIRAISHI]
Heh...
[IENAGA]
I better go check on Shiraishi.
[USHIYAMA]
Proprietress!
How long are you gonna
keep me waiting?
Well, I have other guests
that I have to attend to.
So, just a bit lon--
[USHIYAMA grunts]
Next time, do as I tell you.
[snorts] What a woman. I better
go outside and cool off.
[gasps]
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
Okay, so, obviously, somebody
who works here is insane.
[IENAGA] It's simple: what I
want is Ushiyama's body.
[SHIRAISHI grunts]
Well, and one other.
The young guest with
the pretty eyes.
Sinna kisara .
Pardon?
[SUGIMOTO]
It means "judo ear".
And you've done a lot
of judo, haven't you?
For whatever reason, I just
never could get into it.
So, you know a
little judo, huh?
[SUGIMOTO]
This guy's amazing.
It's like his center of gravity
is below the ground!
At this rate, we'll end
up killing each other.
I like you. Drinks on me.
Let's go!
[USHIYAMA] Rice curry
made with Ezo venison.
Osoma .
No, it's okay. See?
It's the osoma you can eat.
[ASIRPA groans]
What's wrong?
[ASIRPA]
It's so hinna !
[USHIYAMA] How about a
little drinking competition?
Keep these coming, would ya?
[USHIYAMA chuckles]
Did you know...
...the samurai who founded
the beer factory?
He was an officer named Hisanari
Murahashi, and he was with the
new government who
fought Toshizou Hijikata
in the Battle of Hakodate!
You know what he said?
He said he's mad
about losing the war,
but that his enemy's
beer is delicious!
Yeah? Hijikata said that?
Yeah! Okay, maybe he didn't,
but I bet that he would
if he was still alive!
[ASIRPA]
Hm?
[grunts]
Everybody help me!
Stop, it's not
gonna come off.
I'm not Kobutori Jiisan,
you know.
Asirpa, don't do that
to his forehead!
Hey, little miss,
lemme give you some advice.
What's important in life...
are dicks.
I don't know. I saw a dick at
a beach once. It was kinda...
[chuckles]
Well, men shrink when
it gets cold, you know.
It gets bigger and smaller,
did you know that?
I'm not talking
about size, here!
I'm saying that what a woman
really needs to find out,
is if it's the dick
of a gentleman.
That's right!
[USHIYAMA] Hm. Now, let's go.
Dick lecture is over.
The proprietress is
waiting in my room.
[ALL]
Thanks for dinner, sensei!
[USHIYAMA] Hm? Was there a
hole in that wall before?
Secret corridor, huh?
[USHIYAMA]
What is this thing?
Hm... My sweet, where are you?
[SHIRAISHI grunts]
Okay. I'm almost there.
[gasps] Ushiyama! What the
hell are you doing here?
[USHIYAMA]
Huh?
It doesn't matter,
come on, help me out!
The proprietress is someone
we knew from before!
[USHIYAMA]
What did you say?
[SHIRAISHI]
I finally remembered!
She was one of the prisoners!
[USHIYAMA]
Proprietress?
[USHIYAMA mumbles]
Hey... Proprietress. Hehe.
[vomits]
[SHIRAISHI] Think back.
You have to remember!
[SHIRAISHI] All the make-up
kept me from recognizing her.
But that mole by her lip.
Remember the old man
that was a doctor?
The proprietress is one
of the tattooed prisoners.
But wearing women's clothing!
Huh?
[USHIYAMA grunts]
It doesn't matter!
[SHIRAISHI yelps]
[snorts] I'm not leaving
until I screw her!
[USHIYAMA yells]
[SHIRAISHI grunts] You know
that won't work, right?
Come on, we can leave from here!
[USHIYAMA] Proprietress!
Proprietress! Proprietress!
Oh good. His lust has driven
him mad. That's great.
[USHIYAMA]
Proprietress! Proprietress!
From the first
moment I saw her,
I thought she was
truly beautiful.
Such smooth skin.
Such lush hair.
And, these eyes.
[IENAGA] Deep, deep blue.
With just a hint of green.
I want them.
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
Tell me, why were you just
licking Asirpa's eyeballs!
[IENAGA]
Damn it.
I shouldn't have weakened the
gas to keep that kid alive!
Oh no! You've got it
completely wrong!
When she got back,
she seemed ill.
My only thought
was for her health.
I promise, I just came
in to check on her.
Listen, eye-licking monster.
How in the hell did
you get in here?
[gasps]
[SUGIMOTO]
I had the door blocked.
So, tell me how you did it!
[SHIRAISHI grunts] Sugimoto!
Let me in! This hotel's insane!
There's bodies in an
underground torture room!
The proprietress is
a tattooed prisoner!
Remember what I told you?
About the prisoner who was
a doctor and would kidnap
his patients and do
crazy things to them?
This is the same person?
The old guy who believed the
crap about eating animal parts
and killed tons of people?
You were really going to eat
Asirpa's beautiful eyes?
[IENAGA]
Youth, strength, beauty.
The longing for a
fulfilling life.
The fact of the matter is,
people are greedy creatures
who want what they can't have.
That's the human condition,
and you know I'm right.
Nobody's going to buy
any of this crap.
You don't buy it, yourself.
[IENAGA grunts]
However, the part about humans
being greedy is very true.
For instance. I'm fully planning
to rip those tattoos off of you
without a thought.
[gasps]
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh? Where did...?
Shiraishi! She ran!
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
[IENAGA] Everything's been
ruined since those
bastards came here!
[USHIYAMA]
Proprietress!
Proprietress! Proprietress!
[IENAGA] It's the man who's
obsessed with his dick!
[snores]
[SHIRAISHI]
Kiroranke, wake up!
We're getting the hell
out of this murder hotel!
She's here!
[KIRORANKE grunts]
[gasps]
Stay away you mad doctor!
That was a grenade.
[IENAGA coughs]
[gasps]
[IENAGA] Listen to me!
This is the guy you want!
He's a tattooed prisoner, too!
Ushiyama the Undefeated!
[GUEST yells]
[grunting]
This hotel is
useless to me, now.
[IENAGA]
It's time to end it!
[SUGIMOTO] Get the hell
off of me, you asshole!
[grunting]
[USHIYAMA] Shit. It was
just getting good, too.
[IENAGA]
I've got to get out of here.
Shiraishi!
Is that alcohol?
[SUGIMOTO yells]
[SHIRAISHI gasps, grunts]
Shiraishi, what the hell
are you doing here?
So, you finally regained
your senses? What about you?
We were supposed
to meet tomorrow!
Oh, I see. That explains it.
[SHIRAISHI]
Huh?
He's the guy, then.
Immortal Sugimoto.
Of course he is.
[exhales]
[SHIRAISHI yells]
[SHIRAISHI] It looks
like a fire's broken out!
We need to focus on
getting out of here alive.
[USHIYAMA]
Wait.
[SHIRAISHI]
Huh?
Just one thing. I have a
message from the old man.
"Keep us informed
of your whereabouts.
And don't assume that you'll
be able to trick me."
[SHIRAISHI]
Hm.
Huh? My bag!
[USHIYAMA]
What bag?
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
There it is!
[SHIRAISHI pants]
[USHIYAMA]
What's wrong?
[SHIRAISHI]
Run!
There you are! Where the
hell have you been?
B-B-Bomb!
[KIRORANKE]
Huh?
[ALL shout]
[IENAGA breathes weakly]
It's you. You have trained
so much. You understand.
I was beautiful and strong
when I was young.
I wanted to stay...
the best me...
Even if that meant
stealing... from others.
[IENAGA breathes weakly]
When was... your perfection?
[SUGIMOTO coughs]
[ASIRPA gasps]
Where's Dick- sensei ?
Dick- sensei ?!
[gasps]
Dick- sensei ...
Yeah, that's a fish cake.
The military and the
police will be here soon.
We can't stay,
unless you want trouble.
Not on your life.
Let's get outta here and go
meet Nopperabo in Abashiri.
[SUGIMOTO] Looks like
there's not a scrap left of
Ushiyama the Undefeated.
♪
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "Trickster fox!"