[ASIRPA] It's a rawomap ,
a trap for catching fish.
[SUGIMOTO]
Look at all of 'em!
They're Sakhalin sculpin.
And they're in season.
So fatty and delicious.
I'm going to clean the ones
that we'll use for
the stew right here.
Grab your knife and help.
Oh, uh. I left my dagger
and bayonet behind.
If you don't gut a
sculpin right away,
it doesn't taste as good. Go get
your stuff fast, you fool!
[SUGIMOTO]
You're scary you know that?
Why don't we try a shortcut.
[MAKANAKKURU]
Stop. Not another step.
Something I can
help you with?
Look down and you'll see
a rope near your feet.
[MAKANAKKURU] It's a trap.
It's called an amappo .
If you trip the line,
it fires a poison arrow.
Looks like you saved me.
Thank you.
You're related to...
Osoma, right?
I'm her father, yes. Asirpa is
my older sister's child.
[MAKANAKKURU] My niece is a
smart one. I trust her judgment.
If she approves of you, you must
be a respectable person.
[SUGIMOTO]
I'm sorry about before.
I assumed there'd be people
here who wouldn't like me
'cause I'm Japanese.
I guess Asirpa
told you the story.
How the villagers were gathering
gold to fight the Sisam
until it was stolen.
And during that fight,
Asirpa's aca and many
others were killed.
Aca ?
It means "father" in the
language of the Ainu.
Our ancestors found that gold.
It was theirs by right.
But then some foul men
stole it to buy weapons
and that bounty was lost to us.
[SUGIMOTO] Do you have
any idea who could've
stolen the gold nuggets?
No. Most of us believe it's the
wrath of Waka - ush Kamuy ,
goddess of water. Ainu don't
wash their clothes
or defecate in the river.
They go to those lengths to
avoid defiling the waters,
yet we panned for gold there.
[MAKANAKKURU] For an Ainu to
dirty the rivers to make war
is blasphemy to us.
That gold is cursed.
You mark my words.
It's haunted by
demons of the past.
♪
[SUGIMOTO] Huci! Guess what?
We've got a surprise.
Look at all the sculpin
we caught for you.
Hinna , hinna .
Hey. What's she doing, there?
She's offering it to
her guardian spirit.
If someone gives us a gift,
we always offer
it up to them first.
Your guardian spirit goes in and
out of the back of your neck,
right about here.
It's called a turenpe ,
and everyone has one from
the moment that they're born.
It remains with them
for their entire life.
That's said to be the reason
why people have all different
personalities and abilities.
Some can actually see
the guardian spirits.
Huci can, a little.
She's already told me that you
have a very strong turenpe .
Huh. So maybe I have my
guardian spirit to thank for
my reputation as being immortal.
Hey, I just realized, I've never
seen you offer anything up.
In this village,
only the old people do it.
Kids these days.
You little rebel.
[ASIRPA] It's ready. I made
the broth from the sculpin.
It's kinaohaw .
It looks great! Time to dig in!
[HUCI]
Mm. Mm-hm!
Alright, let's eat.
Mm! Mmm! So good!
It's flavorful and rich
without being too heavy.
There's all different
kinds of root vegetables,
instead of just one. Ahh.
I am a fan of sculpin stew.
[SUGIMOTO]
Hey, Asirpa,
Again, this stew
is really tasty,
but I think a touch of miso
would take it over the top!
Would you shut up, Sugimoto?
Put your poop away.
No. Here, take a look.
It's a paste called miso.
[ASIRPA]
Stop that!
It's a disgrace,
that's what it is.
Making her offer poop
to her guardian spirit.
[SUGIMOTO]
It's not poop...
What're you doing?!
What the hell is that thing?
[ASIRPA]
A sutu .
It's a staff used to bring
great pain to the wicked.
And that's you!
[SUGIMOTO]
Wait! Wait! Stop! Stop!
Get that thing away from me!
[SUGIMOTO gibbers]
[CHILDREN laugh]
Hey bud, you put on some
weight in the past few days?
See, I told you.
Bears grow up really fast.
[BOY A]
Asirpa?
Will you do it?
You're the best one
at being super scary.
[ASIRPA]
Okay.
[SUGIMOTO]
What is that?
It's called kisarari ,
which means
"long-eared monster".
You wave it in front of a window
while making horrible noises.
It's just a little game
to scare children.
Pretty effective, actually.
Go ahead. Why don't you try it?
Wait, me?
[SUGIMOTO]
Ahem...
[SUGIMOTO roars terribly]
[ASIRPA] Stop, stop!
You're terrible at this.
Stop it.
Give it to me.
That was embarrassing.
[SUGIMOTO sighs]
[ASIRPA]
Ahem.
--[ASIRPA roars]
--[CHILDREN scream]
[BOY A gasps] Asirpa really
is so good at being scary.
Osoma even peed her pants.
Please, Asirpa. Let me
regain my honor.
In that case. Go. Show me
what you can really do!
Ahem.
[yells]
[CHILDREN laughing, chattering]
[ASIRPA] That's it!
Good. Well done, Osoma!
--[BOTH snoring]
--[distant howling]
[MAKANAKKURU]
Listen. Can you hear that?
It's a sound you
don't hear often.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[MAKANAKKURU] A howl like
a dog's, but longer and lower.
A wolf.
I've seen a white
wolf up here twice,
and both times it saved Asirpa.
Is there a story there?
Ah, I see. So, that
howl was Retar.
I'd wondered if it was.
Asirpa and her father
found that wolf while
they were out hunting,
back when he was
still just a pup.
They thought he
looked like a snowman,
so they named him Retar,
which means "white".
Those two were always together.
After her father was killed,
Asirpa and Retar would go off
into the mountains
on their own.
But it couldn't last.
They belonged to two
different worlds.
[howling]
[ASIRPA gasps]
What's that howling?
Wait, is that your...?
No! Please don't listen!
[ASIRPA] No, stop!
Get back to your shed!
Retar, don't go!
[MAKANAKKURU]
He couldn't do it.
He couldn't be
someone's pet dog.
Retar.
[howls]
[MAKANAKKURU]
He was born to live free.
A proud Horkewkamuy .
[ASIRPA] Come back, Retar!
Please, you can't leave me, too!
What am I supposed
to do without you?
[ASIRPA sobs]
[ASIRPA]
Retar, come back!
Aca !
[MAKANAKKURU]
I know she may seem grown up,
but the truth is, Asirpa is
a lonely little girl.
After that happened,
she never smiled anymore.
But here lately, she's happier.
I think being in the
mountains with you
has brought her some joy.
[HUCI speaks Ainu]
[SUGIMOTO]
Hm?
[speaking Ainu]
I think I know what
you're saying.
It's beautiful. You love
her so much, don't you?
The whole village does.
[SUGIMOTO]
Farewell.
[ASIRPA]
He left without telling me?
I will never forgive him.
I won't feel right till I whack
him in the head with a sutu .
[ASIRPA]
There's no sign it was used.
So, he went to town
and didn't come back?
This doesn't feel right.
It'll be really hard to find
him in that huge town, though.
What do I do? I've got to try.
[whistling]
[ASIRPA] If I keep playing my
deer flute on this deer path,
then maybe he'll think
there's game here
and he'll come to hunt it.
[SUGIMOTO]
Hey, big guy.
Huh? Oh, it's you again.
Has anything strange
happened lately?
[MAN A]
Hm. Yeah, one thing.
A girl who works at a place
a friend of mine owns
was badly hurt by a customer.
That kind of thing
isn't too rare, though.
[MAN A] Well, the customer
had weird tattoos.
That's what you were looking
for the last time, right?
[SUGIMOTO]
Hm.
[OLD WOMAN] I'll go get the
girl and bring her down.
You wait here. Have a nice,
hot bowl of herring soba.
Our herring soba is
the best in town.
This looks good.
The broth's nice and thick,
it's just right for a boy
from Kanto like me.
[SUGIMOTO] And the subtle
sweetness of the herring
as it melts in your mouth.
She wasn't kidding.
This is delicious.
Oh! That was hinna ,
hinna alright.
[door clatters]
So, which man was it?
Who was asking about
the strange tattoos?
It was the one
in the army cap.
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[grunting]
Don't move!
[KOUHEI]
On your knees.
If I shoot you like this,
a bullet might hit
some unsuspecting soul as
it comes out of your face.
[YOUHEI grunts]
Get back. It's time
for him to die.
[gunshot]
[TSURUMI] That's quite enough!
Don't kill him just yet.
You should think of me as
your personal Grim Reaper.
At any moment I
should desire it,
I can extinguish the
candle of your life.
[SUGIMOTO] Look, I was just
hired by a regular of the whore
who got hurt.
"Go find a man with weird
tattoos and make him pay,"
that's what he said. I ask
around about the guy,
and suddenly I'm surrounded
by men with guns.
So, of course I'm
gonna run, right?
I mean, who wouldn't?
[SUGIMOTO]
He's not buyin' it.
I need to find a way
out of here, quick.
Tell me, do you like sweets?
[SUGIMOTO]
Uh...
[TSURUMI]
These are kushi dango ,
from Hanazono Park in Otaru.
It's good. Been so long since
I've had anything sweet,
I'm surprised I'm not drooling.
[TSURUMI]
Mh-hm.
Immortal, Immortal.
One of my men was found
half-dead by the riverside.
But he wrote those
words with his fingers.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
Thanks for the snack.
Is that the exit over there?
[TSURUMI] You're the one who
left Private Ogata like that,
aren't you?
And that makes you
the Immortal Sugimoto.
Sit down.
You guys look alike,
you know thta?
Which one of you was it
that hit me with the gun?
You should mark up your face,
then people could
tell you apart.
I'm going to kill you.
[SUGIMOTO] Look, I'm sorry,
but you've got the wrong guy.
My name isn't Sugimoto.
[TSURUMI] I saw Immortal
Sugimoto once at Port Arthur.
Even from far away,
I was in awe of his ferocity.
A demon on the battlefield,
merciless and unstoppable.
I know it was you
who I saw that day.
After that display
at the soba house,
there's no doubt in my mind.
Except, I was in the Second.
I wasn't even at Port Arthur.
Looks like you really
do have the wrong guy.
Why would Private Ogata
do something as foolish
as attacking the
Immortal Sugimoto?
The only reason I can think of
is you had one of the tattoos
that show where the
missing gold is hidden.
I believe that's why you
tried to flee from us.
Because you were afraid
we'd figure that out.
You have one of the
tattooed skins, don't ya?
Why don't you tell
me where it is?
Wait, gold? And tattoos?
Yeah, I dunno what
you're talking about.
Hey, buddy, what do you think?
Is your boss alright
in the head?
Actually, a shell blew away
a little chunk of my brain.
[YOUHEI laughs]
[SUGIMOTO laughs]
No reaction at all.
Not even so much as a blink.
That's impressive. I knew it.
You are Immortal Sugimoto.
But if you're immortal and
I can't blow out the candle
of your life the way I
had promised, it'll be
a lot less gratifying, but I'll
just have to chew that
candle from the top down.
[ASIRPA] This is one of
Sugimoto's socks.
He left it behind.
You stand out, Retar,
so we'll wait for nightfall.
[TSURUMI] There's only one way
for you to survive this one,
my friend. Agree to
come and work for me.
I'm afraid I lost many of my
men out on the battlefield.
I need more of 'em now.
I have a little under a hundred
men searching all of Hokkaido.
It isn't even close to enough.
[SUGIMOTO] That sounds like
an awful lot of people
to split the gold with,
if you ask me.
The gold goes into
our war chest.
The weapons and ammo
we stole from Asahikawa
aren't going to last forever.
[SUGIMOTO] What exactly
are you planning to do?
[TSURUMI] We're going to buy
weapons from an American.
The very latest weapons,
gathered from all
over the world.
We'll start by taking
over the Seventh.
After that, we'll assume
control of all the major ports
that control the flow of
goods to the mainland.
Hokkaido will be ours.
We were heroes
on the battlefield,
but when we arrived back home,
we became vagrants.
Think, did you gain
anything from fighting?
Or did you lose far more?
I want a brave
soldier like you
standing beside
me in this fight.
Join us and live
like the god you are.
This is a waste of time.
[TSURUMI] Maybe I'll bite
down on that candle, then.
[ASIRPA]
He's inside there?
Okay, go.
[SHIRAISHI yawns]
[SHIRAISHI yells]
It's a monster!
What the...?
You're not Sugimoto.
Aren't you?
You're the Scat King.
I'm Yoshitake Shiraishi,
the Escape King!
Huh? Wait just a minute.
Aren't you that
Ainu kid from before?
[SHIRAISHI yells]
Don't eat him.
Retar would never
mistake a scent.
Now, where is Sugimoto?
I don't know! He's not
with me! I'm alone!
[ASIRPA] But, that doesn't
make any sense.
We followed the
scent from his sock.
Why would his scent
lead us here to you?
[SHIRAISHI]
His sock?
Wait a minute.
That has to be it.
We accidentally exchanged socks!
That's disgusting.
Hold on now, lemme guess.
Sugimoto left and
betrayed you, didn't he?
I'm betting he up and
ran off with those skins.
Shut up.
Yeah, I see now,
that explains it.
So, that rumor going
around is about Sugimoto.
What rumor?
Tell me what you mean.
[SHIRAISHI] Yesterday, a man
with a big scar on his face
got in a huge
fight in the street
before being taken to
the Seventh's hideout.
[ASIRPA gasps]
And if those
bastards got 'im,
he's probably dead by now, so--
Take me to where he is.
This poison can kill
a bear in ten steps.
But you'll die before
you can take one.
[SHIRAISHI groans]
[SHIRAISHI]
Fine! Fine!
Just stop pointing
that thing at me!
Scary kid. What the hell?
Hang on a second. Gonna wash
my face so I can wake up.
[ASIRPA]
My bad feeling was right.
Be okay, Sugimoto.
What's wrong?
[ASIRPA gasps]
He ran.
[pants]
[SHIRAISHI gasps, yells]
[ASIRPA] Retar can run all
through the night if he has to.
You can hide in the
bottom of a latrine
and he'll still find you.
Keep running if
you want, Escape King.
You'll never escape
a Horkewkamuy .
No point even trying.
[SHIRAISHI groans]
[KOUHEI] You still alive,
kushi dango boy?
[YOUHEI] Is this really
Immortal Sugimoto?
I'm not so sure.
[KOUHEI] You don't think we
got the wrong guy, do you?
His face had swelled up to
twice its size after I beat him
so hard, but it looks like the
swelling's gone down now.
If it's really him,
we could rip out his guts,
and he'd be
healed by morning.
But if we kill him,
we won't be able to find
out where the tattoos are.
Let's stop wasting time and
just start chopping fingers off
one by one until he
finally spits it out.
[SUGIMOTO] You're the
one who hit me in front of
the soba place, right?
Huh? Gotta speak up.
No worries.
I'll put a mark on you so
people can tell you apart.
Huh? Shut your mouth,
you insolent little asshole!
[grunting]
I'm the Immortal Sugimoto!
♪
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "Race".