[grunting]
Shiraishi! Pick up the gun!
I'm trying, okay?
[SHIRAISHI yells]
[SHIRAISHI]
Hey! You stupid... Take a hike.
Shoe's on the other foot now!
Don't you move a muscle!
[TANIGAKI]
Not so fast. Drop it.
[ASIRPA gasps]
[SUGIMOTO]
Listen, bastard.
You are not using her as
a human shield, damn it!
Let her go!
Stay back!
You coward! Who uses an
innocent child as a damn shield?
"Innocent"?
This girl was carrying one
of the tattooed skins.
She may be a kid,
but she's not innocent.
He'll shoot me too. My life's
not worth much to him.
Then, he'll shoot you.
Don't try to fight him.
We should get out of here.
[TETSUZOU] You can't
trust women, Tanigaki.
Don't listen to her.
Put the gun down or die!
I'll put a damn bullet in
all three of you! try me!
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
[SUGIMOTO]
Shiraishi.
[SHIRAISHI]
Huh?
[SUGIMOTO]
I'm sorry. But drop the gun.
Please, let the girl go.
I don't want her to see this.
[TETSUZOU grunts]
Fair enough. Help me out.
I need something
to tie 'em up with.
[gasps]
Take her away. Far enough that
she can't hear the screams.
Stop it! Let go! Sugimoto!
Shiraishi! Don't kill them!
What the hell?
Oh, right, he's the Escape King.
[SHIRAISHI] Okay, we're still
alive, but now what?
We lost all our weapons!
[SUGIMOTO] We'll hide someplace
close by 'til we can catch
them off guard. Then we
take back Asirpa and run!
♪
[TETSUZOU] Tanigaki!
Careful, they got away!
--[ASIRPA gasps] He's alive!
--[TANIGAKI] Quiet.
I need to get out of the woods.
I'll be safer if I find
a better vantage point.
[TANIGAKI breathes heavily]
[ASIRPA grunts]
[ASIRPA gasps]
Stop walking!
Would you stop squirming?
There's a trap ahead!
Watch out! It's an amappo !
[TANIGAKI grunts]
[ASIRPA grunts]
[TANIGAKI groans]
You have to untie me!
[gasps]
[ASIRPA] That arrowhead's
coated with wolfsbane.
We need to get it out quick.
[TANIGAKI]
Hm?
If we don't, you'll die!
[TANIGAKI grunts]
I feel like my leg's on fire!
Ainu poisons don't
have an antidote.
Our only choice is to cut
out the poisoned flesh.
[TANIGAKI]
Fine!
Do it!
[TANIGAKI screams]
[SHIRAISHI]
Where did they go?
[SUGIMOTO]
This way, moron.
[ASIRPA gasps]
Got hit by an
arrow trap, did he?
[ASIRPA]
I cut away the poisoned flesh,
but I don't know if
he'll make it or not.
Can we stop this?
We didn't come here to kill
each other, after all.
[gun clicks]
[TETSUZOU] Tanigaki,
you wait right here.
I swear I'll kill that
wolf and bring it back.
[ASIRPA] I can't reason
with him. He's obsessed.
[TETSUZOU]
If what he said is true,
you can bring the
wolf here can't you?
You're going to help
me catch that wolf
and then I'll let you go.
[ASIRPA] Put me down!
Stop it! This is insane!
Retar is the only
wolf of his kind!
Are you really going wipe
out the only Horkewkamuy
just to sell his hide
for some filthy money?
Ezo wolf's are already extinct!
Their race will never revover.
The sin of letting
them go extinct...
...is one that everyone who
lives in this land shares.
I don't give a damn
about the money.
I just want to be the
last hunter in the world
to face off with an Ezo wolf.
[TETSUZOU grunts]
[ASIRPA grunts]
[TETSUZOU] I don't care if
you wanna scream and cry,
but if you're gonna threaten
to kill yourself, don't bother.
You couldn't bite your
tongue off if you tried.
[ASIRPA]
I'm not going to kill myself.
I just don't want Retar
to become a Wenkamuy .
Is that the thing where if
an animal kills a human,
they turn into an evil
god and go to hell?
I wouldn't worry. I doubt human
lives are worth that much.
Besides, this is a battle
between beasts.
Nothing more.
Though I'm the only beast
that's coming back alive.
I'll end it with a single shot.
He won't suffer.
[ASIRPA gasps]
I'll be damned. My plan
worked like a charm.
[TETSUZOU]
He's running so I can't aim,
does he understand
how a gun works?
A true adversary. Worthy of
being the last of his kind!
Stay away, Retar!
Now!
[TETSUZOU groans]
It looks like I win.
[TETSUZOU grunts]
[RYUU barks]
That's enough. Good boy.
You just stay here and
keep me warm, all right?
I see. So you had a lady friend.
Thought this was a duel.
You're not playing by the rules.
I should've known better, huh?
Just like I always say,
you can't trust women, Ryuu.
Well. This isn't so bad.
[ASIRPA]
Huh?
[gasps]
--[ASIRPA sighs]
--[howling]
All this time,
you had a family, huh?
That's what called you
away the night you left me.
[TANIGAKI grunts]
[TANIGAKI]
"May you be born again,
and may you awaken
to pleasant sounds."
[SHIRAISHI] We're seriously
dragging these two along?
[ASIRPA] If we leave him
out in the snow, he'll die.
And if we leave the dog,
it'll stay there forever.
[SHIRAISHI groans]
Well, I'm done!
I'm gonna take a little break
till Sugimoto
catches up with us.
[OSOMA speaks Ainu]
What's that?
She's saying that
your ears look funny.
[SHIRAISHI]
Hm?
Are you sure this is smart?
Well. If my partner wants
to save him that bad,
then I won't stop her.
Later, if he decides
to cross us,
I'll kill the ungrateful
bastard myself.
[ASIRPA] This is deer hotpot.
We call it yukohaw . Eat up!
Oh, hinna , hinna . I've never
had venison in soup before.
It's hinna all right.
[ASIRPA chuckles]
Oh no. Sure hope you
don't use osoma .
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
Disgusting. I don't suppose
you have some with you now?
What? Miso? It's right here.
[ASIRPA laughs]
Again, Sugimoto?
You can't get enough of
that filthy osoma , can you?
[SHIRAISHI groans]
Get it off!
Wow, he is really
going at it.
You got honey coming
out of your head?
[ASIRPA]
Osoma's great!
[SUGIMOTO]
It's not poop.
[SHIRAISHI]
Ow! Why aren't you helping me?
[ASIRPA]
This is salmon ruype .
We make it by hanging
raw meat or fish
from a tree until it freezes.
It's half frozen so the
texture's real crunchy!
But if you keep chewing,
then it melts in your mouth.
Juicy!
Well, of course! " Ruype "
does mean "melted food"!
I get it!
Everything else in this place
is frozen, so your meat is too!
[speaking Ainu]
Can you... translate that?
It's a paskuma
about fish. A legend.
She's talking about something
that happened in Hidaka,
Kushiro, Shiraoi-- everywhere.
Delegates from each village
took to the sea and brought all
the gold they had
gathered to one place.
After this continued
for several years,
villagers could no
longer catch salmon,
and life became very difficult.
The Ainu held a meeting
and agreed to stop
gathering the gold.
After that, they hid it away,
and to prevent conflict,
they forbade speaking of it.
Time passed.
People grew old and died.
Eventually, only one
man was left
who knew the
location of the gold.
And of course, he's dead.
Murdered by Nopperabo, huh?
[SHIRAISHI]
H-Hold up. Something's wrong.
This is our gold you're
talking about, right?
That means they spent
years gathering the stuff
from all over Hokkaido!
[ASIRPA]
I don't know.
I've never heard this
paskuma before.
Then what if this
legend is actually true?
We thought we were looking
for 20 kan worth of gold,
but it could be much
more than that!
[TANIGAKI]
There is more.
[SHIRAISHI, SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
There's more than
you could imagine.
Like she said,
that story has been passed
down in secret by the Ainu.
My commander
confirmed it himself.
I trust his judgement.
He's an intelligence officer,
and a thorough one, at that.
[SUGIMOTO]
You mean, Lt. Tsurumi?
[TSURUMI] Nopperabo wanted to
make sure no one could retrace
his steps to guess the
location of the gold,
so he spread false information.
Twenty kan is a reasonable
amount for one man to carry.
But in reality,
there was so much gold.
It's more than any
man could ever carry.
If Lt. Tsurumi is correct,
there could be a thousand times
more gold than you thought.
[SHIRAISHI yelps]
Twenty thousand?
But this Tsurumi guy seems
kind of crazy, if you ask me.
He said he was gonna take
over the 7th Division base
in Asahikawa, right? Then what?
March to Tokyo and stage a coup?
Is that really the smartest
thing to do with all that money?
Why fight when he could split
it with all of his friends
and still live a life of luxury?
Why does the 7th Division
mean so much to him?
The Siege of Port Arthur, maybe.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[TSURUMI] Those Maxim guns sound
like they're leading a march
to hell itself.
The fools who ordered
this meaningless assault
should have to
hear it themselves!
[TSURUMI]
Hit that bunker with a grenade!
[SOLDIER A]
Yes, sir.
[TSURUMI]
Forgive me.
[RUSSIAN SOLDIERS scream]
Charge!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
We won the battle.
Ten thousand went up that hill,
but by the time we finally
took hill 203,
less than half remained.
The chief of staff was obsessed
with a frontal assault
so he could take the
glory for himself.
Once he saw all the lives
he wasted, he took his own.
The government blamed
his suicide on what was
left of our division.
We received no medals, no money.
The army treated
us like outcasts.
But Lt. Tsurumi still
believed in our future.
[TSURUMI] We will form
a military republic!
I will be its leader and you
will be my elite guards!
We can't just pass out
the gold to everyone.
Instead, we will use it to open
up a weapons factory here,
in resource-rich Hokkaido.
[THOMAS] Apologies, but good
guns don't come cheap.
On your meager budget,
I'm afraid this is the
best I can provide.
If you want to build that
weapons factory of yours,
Mr. Tsurumi, then I say
the sooner the better.
I'll gladly buy your products
and sell them all
over the world.
War is very
profitable after all.
And business is booming.
[TSURUMI] Children who
have lost their fathers,
fathers who have
lost their sons,
and wives who have
lost their husbands.
We shall offer them
all stable employment.
We'll save them from
spending their lives
starving in this frozen land,
we will provide them salvation.
Although it won't
bring them back,
this is the least we can do
to honor our fallen comrades!
[TANIGAKI] Lt. Tsurumi is
carrying a great burden
on his shoulders
for his fellow men.
I don't know what
you're planning to do
with all that gold, but it
had better be something
worth fighting for.
[SHIRAISHI]
Hey, Sugimoto.
[SUGIMOTO]
Hm?
[SHIRAISHI]
You're not gonna call it quits
'cause of that little
sob story right?
You're not switching
sides are you?
[SUGIMOTO]
No. I've already killed his men.
I can't turn back now.
Even if I did agree with him,
it would never work out.
And, anyway, I want that gold.
That's the Sugimoto
I know and love!
Come on. I'm keeping a promise
to my partner, that's all.
[USHIYAMA grunts]
[USHIYAMA]
I need a woman... Now!
That man is a beast. What if
someone calls the police?
[HIJIKATA] The hard labor at
Abashiri Prison was so severe
that it proved fatal
for many inmates.
Ushiyama, on the other hand,
complained that it wasn't
enough to keep him in shape.
[door clatters]
Nagakura. Call the beast for me.
We're going into town.
[MEN grunting]
[MAN B]
Please forgive me!
You should probably
think twice
about who you pick
a fight with, punk!
[USHIYAMA]
Move.
Eh?
[MAN A gasps]
I'm gonna take off
for a bit, all right?
You go have a cup of tea or do
whatever you geezers like to do.
You call me that one more time,
and I'll carve you up.
Ooh. Damn! The toughest
swordsman from the old
Shinsengumi has a temper to
match his reputation, huh?
[USHIYAMA laughs]
Let the man go.
If Ushiyama can't get a
lady every now and then,
he loses his mind.
Like you said, he's a beast.
Be careful or he might
even come after you.
[SHIRAISHI hums]
[MAN C] Hey, mister.
You back already?
I don't have any news,
but I've got ladies.
I could find prettier girls
than that in a barn.
You really know how
to piss me off, huh?!
[SHIRAISHI]
Hm!
[SHIRAISHI] Maybe I'll ask
around a high-class
brothel today. It's not
wasting money if I'm doing it
to find the gold, right?
[SHIRAISHI giggles]
[gasps]
[USHIYAMA] Well, fancy meeting
you here, Shiraishi.
Why are you running away,
old friend?
I just wanna have a little chat!
[SHIRAISHI]
Crap! Crap! Crap!
Ushiyama is the last escaped
convict I need right now!
[SHIRAISHI]
Hey, big guy!
[MAN C]
Huh?
[SHIRAISHI] That's him!
The guy you're looking for!
He's the one who hurt
your girl the other day!
Now's your chance! Get him!
[MAN C] You got some nerve
showing your face here.
But if you want an ass-kicking
that bad, you got one.
Yeah! Take him down a notch!
[MAN E]
You got this!
[WOMAN A]
Save some for me!
[ALL yell]
[SHIRAISHI]
That didn't even slow him down!
C'mon gimmie a break!
Gotta think of somethin!
Aw yeah! I'll see you in hell!
[SHIRAISHI yelps]
[horse whines]
[MAN F]
Get out of the way! Hurry!
[USHIYAMA grunts]
[SHIRAISHI]
Are you kidding me?
This guy's tossing
around horses now?
If that didn't faze him,
then nothing will!
This guys like a rampaging bull!
[gasps]
[KOUHEI]
Hm?
[SHIRAISHI]
The 7th Division?
Something wrong?
What's the big hurry?
[SOLDIER D] You're acting
awfully suspicious.
[SOLDIER E] Hey, anybody have
those wanted posters?
[gasps]
You guys gotta help me!
That maniac said I stole his
money at the bath house
and he's trying to kill me!
He's got these weird
tattoos all over his body!
He must be some kinda criminal!
[gasps]
♪
[NARRATOR] Next time:
"Eyes of a Murderer".