Bitter.
[MALE SOLDIER A]
We're gonna starve down here.
If I gotta take a bite out
of a Russian's white ass
to stay alive, I'll do it.
I am not gonna die.
[MALE SOLDIER B]
Ready, Men? Charge!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[SUGIMOTO yells]
[yelling continues]
[RUSSIAN SOLDIER A gasps]
[SUGIMOTO]
C'mon!
[RUSSIAN SOLDIERS grunting]
Just try and kill me!
--[SUGIMOTO] Die!
--[RUSSIAN SOLDIER G screams]
I'm the Immortal Sugimoto!
[GOTOU] Hey, c'mon, pal.
I'm talkin' to you here.
Saichi Sugimoto,
can you hear me?
You just got back from the
war with Russia, right?
So why the hell are you here?
I heard you were so tough
they called you the
Immortal Sugimoto.
Never woulda guessed an
easygoing guy like you
was such a monster. They say you
clawed your way up from the pits
of hell, leaving a mountain
of corpses in your wake.
Bayonets, machine guns, even
cannonballs couldn't kill you.
So, let's hear it.
That true or what?
I'm just sayin' it's fishy.
If you did all that stuff,
they'd give you a medal or
a pension or some crap, but here
ya are lookin' for gold.
[SUGIMOTO] Yeah, well, I got
pissed off and beat the crap
out of a superior officer,
so they weren't feeling
too charitable.
[laughs]
Well, that's a shame!
Y'know. I got an
interesting story, too.
It's about gold, so it'll
probably tickle your fancy.
Now you keep this
one between us.
I'm only lettin' you in on the
secret 'cause I like ya, kiddo.
Back in the day, you could
find gold all over Hokkaido.
Their riverbanks had
pieces as big as soybeans.
People were comin' back with
30 monme worth of the stuff,
day after day. That's what I
call a "gold rush," my friend.
Around that time, some Ainu were
storing up tons of this gold
to fight the Japanese,
who were still oppressing
them even after the
Meiji restoration,
forbidding them from
hunting and fishing,
and stealing their land.
[GOTOU] Ha,ha. Hell, 'least
they were rich, right?
And then one man stole it all.
Killed every last Ainu
guardin' it, the maniac.
Twenty kan in solid gold!
That's enough to buy
every brothel in Otaru,
with plenty to spare!
Anyway, the police
caught wind of the story,
and the killer had to
hide the gold in Hokkaido.
And then he got caught
before he could tell anyone
where he stashed
his treasure.
They threw him into
Abashiri Prison,
at the ends of the earth,
sentenced to death.
He wanted to tell his
comrades on the outside
where the gold was, but he
never wrote a letter.
The guards would probably
just steal it you see.
He knew everyone was
looking for this gold.
Those guards tried
every trick in the book,
but they couldn't get
a word outta the man.
In the end, one of the
guards turned out to be
a real sick bastard.
Just to make sure the man
wouldn't escape, he cut
a tendon in his leg!
What would you do, if that
hidden gold was yours?
If you were locked up in most
heavily-guarded prison
in Japan, how would you get a
message out with all those
guards breathin' down your neck?
What'd he do? Just tell me.
He hid the message on
a body... Or bodies.
He tattooed the flesh of
cellmates with a code
that revealed the location
of the treasure.
He mixed coal with saliva.
And with a makeshift needle,
he formed a map across their
skin that only his friends on
the outside could understand.
When it was over, he had
only one thing to say.
"I've given you the answer,
now break out of this prison
and half the gold is yours."
[SUGIMOTO]
That doesn't make sense.
Just send a coded
letter with them.
Tattoos are too conspicuous.
[GOTOU]
That's what you think.
It wasn't until later they
understood the truth
behind the tattoos.
They're all unique,
so you can't crack the code
unless you had all
of 'em together.
Some disreputable
soldiers heard the rumors
about the tattoos and
had the prison hand over
the inmates, sayin' they
needed a transfer.
The military wanted
that gold, too.
But that was the prisoners
chance to escape.
They knew someone
would get greedy,
and take all of them
out of the prison,
thinkin' that they could
figure out the code.
As you might guess, the
criminals killed all the guards,
and disappeared into the woods.
Then what?
I dunno.
So nobody found the
prisoners or the gold?
[GOTOU] Nope. That's the end of
the story. Pretty crazy, huh?
All a' that gold, just out
there waiting. Real pity.
[SUGIMOTO] You seem to know
an awful lot about this.
Who told you the story?
[SUGIMOTO]
Another one of your tall tales.
Like that Ezo wolf you said
you saw. They all died out.
It's been years now.
[GOTOU snores]
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[SUGIMOTO sighs]
I'm freezing.
[TORAJI]
Saichi, you should come with me.
There's still plenty of gold
to be found in Hokkaido.
You don't have anything
tying you down, right?
I need to try and make
money for my family.
Umeko. She loses more of
her eyesight every day.
There's no time.
It makes me sad to think about
her not being able to see
her child grow up.
I have to try, Saichi.
Yeah, I know.
They say America has the best
eye doctors in the world.
I did the math.
The ship passage and
the operation would cost
about 200 yen.
That's a lot, but one lucky day
of panning for gold and I'm set.
Once this war's over,
our relations with America
are probably going to
get worse. There's no time.
Saichi, please take
care of Umeko.
Nobody will want to marry a
woman with failing vision.
Not with a child, too.
You're my best friend.
I'm begging you.
Don't say that.
It'll work out, Toraji.
[gasps]
[TORAJI] I can't go back
with you. I'm sorry.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
Wait! No!
You're family's waiting
for you, damn it! Toraji!
Stop!
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[sighs]
[clicking]
Aw. Crap. It ain't your fault,
but I said too much.
Go ahead and try. Let's see
if I'm immortal or not.
[gasps]
[GOTOU groans]
All right. Now we're
locked and loaded.
[GOTOU shouts]
[SUGIMOTO]
I'll be damned.
That crazy story of his might
not be so crazy after all.
[SUGIMOTO]
He already came after me once.
If I let him go, he might do it
again. It's kill or be killed.
--[SUGIMOTO gasps]
--[crow caws]
Okay, that's weird.
[SUGIMOTO] What happened?
Why are you buried like that?
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[gasps]
A brown bear.
It took one bite and
buried the rest for later.
His neck was broken.
The thing killed him before
he could even scream.
Some luck. Oh well.
[SUGIMOTO]
Wait. What the...?
Is that what I
think it is? No way.
[SUGIMOTO] A tattoo. You were
one of the prisoners all along.
That about settles it, then.
No wonder that old drunk
knew so much about the gold.
So, this is the
treasure map, huh?
Or at least a piece of it.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[SUGIMOTO]
Better get moving.
I can't leave him out here.
When that bear comes back,
it'll eat him for dinner.
That means no more tattoo.
--[clattering]
--[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[SUGIMOTO] A bear cub?
It's alone? No, hold on.
That means the mother must be...
[bear growls]
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
[gasps]
[SUGIMOTO]
I'm screwed.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[ASIRPA]
Move away.
The poison I used is made
from red stingray spine and
wolfsbane root, so it acts fast,
but the bear can still lash out.
That girl... She's an Ainu.
[SUGIMOTO]
Is it dead?
[ASIRPA] Its hairs aren't
standing on end anymore, so yes.
What're you doing?
Cutting out the part where
the poison arrow hit.
Otherwise, the poison will
spoil the meat and the fur.
He was killed?
Uh, yeah. He was gutted
and buried in the snow.
The mother bear ate his insides.
Mother bear?
There was a cub in a tree
and she burst out of a hole
over there to protect it.
That's not right.
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
[ASIRPA] When a bear first
comes out of hibernation,
its stomach is shrunken,
so it can't eat yet.
Even if it did attack a
human to protect its cub,
it couldn't eat them.
Look. The stomach is empty.
So, you're saying he was
attacked by a different bear?
It's a " matakarip ".
It means "those who
wander in the winter".
If it ate meat,
then it has to be one.
They're bears who
missed hibernation.
Very aggressive.
What are you going to
do with that man's body?
[SUGIMOTO] I'm not sure.
Take him to a town?
[ASIRPA] Bad idea. A matakarip
won't give up so easily,
not after it's had
a taste of meat.
Wherever you take its dinner,
it's sure to follow you.
You don't want to lead a wild
bear into a town, do you?
Forget him.
Not a chance!
[ASIRPA] Hm? I didn't realize
he meant so much to you.
Is he a family member of yours?
It's complicated, okay?
Fine, if you think you
can kill that bear.
You are a soldier I guess.
[SUGIMOTO]
Yeah, but I fought Russians,
not monster bears.
That's not exactly the same.
[ASIRPA]
Night will be here soon.
If you're having
second thoughts,
I wouldn't advise fighting a
bear in pitch darkness.
The weak will be eaten.
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
I've got an interesting
story to share.
I dunno how much of it is true,
but it all checks out so far.
That means I can't let
this skin get eaten.
It looks like you're
used to hunting bears.
I could use your help.
It was the dying wish
of my best friend.
I need money,
no matter what.
I get it. You think I'm nuts.
I didn't believe the
story at first, either.
I'll do it.
You will?
My father. He was one of
the Ainu who was killed.
The story must be true.
And you're sure?
[ASIRPA] We can talk more later.
For now, gather firewood.
[SUGIMOTO]
Are the bears afraid of fire?
[ASIRPA] No. We're not
trying to keep it away.
This is to give us light
so we can shoot it.
We'll set up an ambush using
the corpse here as bait.
[SUGIMOTO] If that's the plan,
then I should bring this guy
a little closer to
the fire, right?
[ASIRPA]
How cruel.
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
His tattoo. I get it now.
Get what?
[ASIRPA]
Look closer.
The killer never intended
to split the gold with them.
They had no clue.
The tattoos stretch
around his chest and arms,
but they stop at the
median lines of his body.
The meaning's clear
to any hunter.
This is how you would mark an
animal you were going to skin.
You're saying, the only reason
they were tattooed was so that
they could be skinned later?
[SUGIMOTO]
This is insane.
What kind of man would come
up with a plan like this?
He'll do anything to
protect that gold.
[SUGIMOTO]
If that's how it works,
can't we just skin him
before the bear comes?
[ASIRPA]
No time.
Brown bears don't wander
far from their prey.
[SUGIMOTO]
All right.
Guess we're hunting
a monster bear, then.
Once a brown bear
kills a human,
it can never eat
anything else again.
No longer fearing us, the bear
becomes an evil god.
A Wenkamuy .
[SUGIMOTO] Once they see
how weak we really are,
it's no surprise
they lose their fear.
Its curse will draw it here.
Be ready, and keep
the fire bright.
We're helpless without its
light until the sun rises.
[ASIRPA]
Find some sitat .
[SUGIMOTO]
Find what now?
[ASIRPA]
White birch bark.
It's oily and it burns
for a long time,
so we can use little
pieces of it like a torch.
[SUGIMOTO] We've got nearly
12 hours until dawn.
We're gonna need a
lot more firewood.
Oh, holy shit!
Already? That was fast!
Well, was worth a shot.
Get down and grab its belly!
[ASIRPA grunts]
[SUGIMOTO screams]
[ASIRPA]
That doesn't sound good.
I can't see it, but I think
I know roughly where it is.
Even if I don't hit its vitals,
the poison should do the trick.
[SUGIMOTO]
Don't shoot!
[ASIRPA gasps]
I'm on its belly!
[ASIRPA]
So he's still alive after all.
I have to risk it!
[SUGIMOTO] Wait! Let me
try something first!
Now hold still so
I can stab you!
[ASIRPA grunts]
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[roars]
Damn it! Stop running!
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[growls]
A dog?
[gasps]
[ASIRPA]
Retar.
Careful not to hit
the shoulder blade!
Aim beneath the armpit
and shoot the heart!
Just try and kill me!
I'm the Immortal Sugimoto!
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[ASIRPA]
Hey. Still alive, Sisam ?
[SUGIMOTO]
Yup. I forgot to mention,
I'm pretty hard to kill.
Although it's dangerous,
that is one way to kill a bear.
I'm surprised you
knew the trick, though.
It's an Ainu technique.
[SUGIMOTO] Technique?
That was just instinct!
You think you could
lend me a hand here?
You have quite the talent
for battle. You're brave, too.
Not bad for a Sisam .
[SUGIMOTO]
A what?
[ASIRPA]
A Japanese.
Saishi Sugimoto.
Asirpa.
[SUGIMOTO] You know what
happened to that big white dog?
It was right here, wasn't it?
[ASIRPA]
He's watching.
He's an Ezo wolf.
That so? Then I guess
they're not extinct.
Looked like it was protecting
you from that bear.
[howls]
[ASIRPA] The murder
happened five years ago.
They were transporting
their gold,
when my father and several
other villagers were killed.
Their bodies were cut to pieces.
Their corpses, eaten by animals.
We couldn't salvage much.
At any rate,
that's all I ever heard.
I didn't even know that
the killer had been sent
to Abashiri Prison.
Of course, no one told me
about the tattoos, either.
Maybe they kept quiet
because they wanted
the gold for themselves.
Hey. I was thinking.
Let's find this gold together.
It belongs to your people.
I don't want that much.
Just a small cut is fine.
[ASIRPA]
Find it how exactly?
[SUGIMOTO] We'll hunt down
the tattooed criminals.
Then what? Murder them
and skin them, huh?
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[ASIRPA] This is yours.
Come on, take it.
[SUGIMOTO]
What is it?
The bear's gall bladder.
It should fetch you a good
price as a natural medicine.
No part goes to waste.
We'll eat the meat, of course,
then sell the pelt and use
the fat as a salve for burns.
Or you can, since you're
the one who killed it.
We worked together.
You're entitled to half.
I'll rather take
the mother bear.
Since the other one's
eaten human flesh.
Ainu don't eat the meat or
take the pelts of a bear
that killed someone.
Bears that do bad things
become evil gods
and are sent to a hell
called Teyne Pokna Mosir .
I don't want to kill anyone.
[SUGIMOTO] If you kill
people you go to hell, huh?
Then they'll reserve a
special place for me.
Y'know, something
just came to mind.
This guy's been
living in hiding.
That means it's likely
nobody's found the gold yet.
Listen, Miss Asirpa, it's your
call, but the man who killed
your father is probably
still alive in that prison.
I'd bet that the government
won't have him killed
until they find that gold.
That means as soon as someone
does find it, he's good as dead.
Now, this may be an odd
way of looking at things.
If you ask me, finding that
gold would be a fine way
to avenge your
father's murder.
Let's be honest.
You already knew that.
That's why you helped me.
I'll be the one getting
my hands dirty.
All I need is your knowledge.
I get my money,
you get your revenge.
[SUGIMOTO]
Our destinations are different,
but our path is the same.
If the two of us team up,
we'll be unstoppable.
♪
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "Nopperabo."