[ASIRPA gasps]
[ASIRPA]
What... what is this?
[HENMI]
Oops. I...
What's wrong?
[HENMI]
I left it there.
[gasps]
Sugimoto!
I think the prisoner might
actually be here at the fishery!
Huh?
[ASIRPA]
Sugimoto?
♪
Hey, so what is it you
wanted to show me?
Uh... It's, uh...
It's just up here.
[HENMI] I need to get
him someplace isolated
where we won't be
interrupted again.
[HENMI]
These are the hammers we use,
and these are the brooms.
They're all tools for shattering
and spreading the leftover parts
of the fish, so they can dry.
Which of these do
you think you'd...
[HENMI] Specifically,
to split my head open.
...like to try out first?
I bet you would prefer
this big, beautiful knife--
[SUGIMOTO]
Listen, sorry to cut you off,
but I said we were leaving.
Hey, thanks for
that herring, though.
[HENMI gasps]
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
The Seventh!
Is it really bad
if they find you?
[SUGIMOTO]
It is...
I don't think I'm what
they came here for, but...
[HENMI]
I see.
So, even the Seventh is
following the bait I set out.
We could have them
hide you in here!
This is the mansion
where the boss lives,
and there are tons
of hiding places!
Sugimoto!
[piano music plays]
I didn't know
you played, Tsurumi.
My family had
money for a time,
but you and I both know
nothing lasts forever.
Life has its ups
and downs, right?
Sometimes you catch many fish,
and sometimes you starve,
especially if your business
depends on mother nature.
[MAGNATE] I don't know
about anything but herring.
I started at the bottom, here,
and worked my way up.
If we ever cease
to catch herring,
both I and this old
place shall rot.
]Unfortunately, friend,
we aren't able to read
the hearts of herring.
Who knows what
their future holds.
But the good news is,
men's hearts are much more
malleable and open
to suggestion.
We can start our very own war
if you'll agree to help me
build my weapons factory.
I do like weapons.
Look at this! I bought this
beauty on the black market
from someone in the military.
Oh! That's something else.
[SUGIMOTO] Are you sure
we can just walk in?
It's an emergency.
C'mon, follow me.
[HENMI] To a place where
we can be alone.
[HENMI gasps]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
Hey, was that a cap?
Do you think it's
Immortal Sugimoto?
[WOMAN A]
Yes, coming.
Oh! Oh, my. Well, what a
cute little guest.
But where are your mother
and father, dear?
You're looking for them?
[ASIRPA grunts]
[WOMAN A]
What's that?
Need to use the bathroom.
[WOMAN A] Hm? You want
to use the restroom?
You gentlemen are the
boss's guests, right?
I'm so glad I found you.
I've been looking everywhere!
I'll get you some tea!
[SOLDIER A]
Outta the way.
I think it really
was Sugimoto.
[HENMI]
Sugimoto? That's not his name.
That guy is a fisherman who's
worked here for years and years.
[SOLDIERS grunting]
[gasps]
So beautiful.
[gunshot]
[BOTH]
Hm?
[HENMI grunts]
[SUGIMOTO]
What's wrong?
[HENMI] How gorgeous.
I will never forget that sight.
Hey, were you shot?
I was so scared!
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
What a coincidence,
the Immortal Sugimoto.
Son of a bitch
So the thieving gull has
dared to enter my mansion?!
You'll make a perfect target!
[gasps]
[MAGNATE laughs]
[SUGIMOTO]
I am immortal!
[HENMI]
Magnificent.
[MAGNATE grunts]
That's enough. Don't kill him.
[HENMI] Oh, Sugimoto.
I was obsessed with the way
my little brother
struggled against death.
I wanted to see it
again and again.
I've killed so many.
The flame of a candle flickers
and gleams most brightly
just before it burns out.
When I see the way
you gleam, my new friend,
it brings it all back.
The way he looked.
[HENMI] I wanted to be
exactly like him. Like you.
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
My friends are just ahead!
They actually got the
whale to the beach!
Let's get to that boat! Come on!
Shiraishi! The Seventh
is on its way!
Get on the boat!
[gasps]
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
Behind you, Sugimoto!
That's Kazuo Henmi, right there!
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
[HENMI grunts]
[yells]
[grunting]
[HENMI]
This is what I wanted.
I'm going to struggle
my hardest for him.
So please, my new friend.
Let me gleam the way he did!
Hurry, Sugimoto!
The Seventh is already here!
[HENMI]
Okay, Immortal Sugimoto.
That is what you call yourself,
isn't that right?
I understand you.
You fight the entire world
because when you die,
you want to die
burning bright.
I have no intention of dying.
I've got a whole lot
more to do first.
Look! There it is!
The stronger your
will to survive is,
the brighter and more
violently you will gleam.
Yeah, sure thing.
I know. Why don't we both
gleam together, then?
Oh, yes! What a
marvelous man you are!
I was born to meet you,
I just know it!
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[HENMI groans]
It's inside me!
[coughs]
Dear Sugimoto,
promise me something.
Promise me that you
won't ever forget me.
Every time I look
at the tattooed skin
I rip off your body,
I'll think of you.
[HENMI grunts]
I'm so glad... that I was born.
[HENMI yelps]
[yells]
[ASIRPA]
A Repun Kamuy !
[HENMI yells]
Asirpa! Shiraishi!
Get in the boat!
That thing's gonna
eat the tattoo!
[SUGIMOTO, SHIRAISHI gasp]
[SHIRAISHI]
The Seventh! Dammit!
Look!
[SHIRAISHI, SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
It's like it's
playing with its food!
What's it doing?
Well, if it's not gonna
eat him, let's grab him.
This is the only
chance we're gonna get!
[HENMI]
No way. Is this happening?
I never would've dared to hope.
A death like this...
[HENMI]
It's the best I could imagine!
Come on, heart.
Don't quit on me, now!
[gasps]
Sugimoto! Hurry up, it's coming!
It'll pull us! Grab on!
[TSURUMI]
We can't catch up with him, now.
Very interesting.
Sugimoto's working
with the Ainu?
Whales that come to
hunt the herring,
and orcas that
come to hunt them.
If you want to eat from
the top of the food chain,
I guess you have to
fight as one of them.
Or become one of the
disgusting creatures
that feed on the bodies.
The carcasses that fall
to the great depths.
You certainly have some
fascinating friends,
don't you, Shiraishi?
Particularly the
Immortal Sugimoto.
[SOLDIER C]
Lieutenant Tsurumi!
[SOLDIER C] Private Ogata
Hyakunosuke disappeared
from the hospital.
And another one, Private First
Class Kouhei Nikaidou,
has apparently been
missing for days.
He's scarier than anybody.
Don't you think?
I won't forget you.
Or how you gleamed.
[TANIGAKI sighs]
Granny. I'm back.
[TANIGAKI]
Hm? What's wrong, Osoma?
Sinna kisar .
[TANIGAKI]
So, Sugimoto's back, then.
[gasps]
[KOUHEI] Granny, you've got
so much tension, dear.
If it isn't Private
First Class Tanigaki.
[gasps]
[OGATA]
So, it was you, then.
A villager told me there
was an injured soldier,
so I thought I'd wait here.
You seem to be making
yourself comfortable.
There was an amappo ,
an arrow trap.
The poison paralyzed me.
Thankfully, the Ainu saved me.
[OGATA] I see you've
recovered enough to walk.
Is there a reason you didn't go
back to Lieutenant Tsurumi?
Today's the first day, though.
Using a staff.
I planned to stay at least long
enough to repay their kindness.
And today was the
first day, huh?
[HUCI grunts]
[TANIGAKI grunts]
The thing is, Corporal Tamai
is still missing.
[TANIGAKI gasps]
Noma and Okada, too.
In fact, none of the others
who were with you came back.
We were tracking some
suspicious hunters.
I got separated from them.
[HUCI grunts]
Sinna kisar ! Sinna kisar !
Sinna kisar !
Ugh. I'm busy!
Osoma, go ahead and take
Granny to your house.
[HUCI grunts]
What exactly was it that
Corporal Tamai told you?
I have no idea what
you're talking about,
but get away
from her, Nikaido.
If you get rough,
you're gonna regret it.
[OGATA] You killed the other
soldiers in your unit,
didn't you, Tanigaki?
[gasps]
Of course not!
[TANIGAKI] This is a
dangerous misunderstanding.
Tell me.
Thinking about your gun?
[TANIGAKI grunts]
You can make a jump for it,
but without this,
it won't do you much good.
[gasps]
I'm begging you, Ogata.
Please, just don't hurt them.
Just a li'l joke.
Testing your reaction.
You really are such a
terrible liar, Tanigaki.
If you want to spend some
time repaying your debt here,
that's fine. I'll pretend
I never found you.
Let's go, Nikaidou.
[OGATA]
Oh, right, by the way.
Have you seen Immortal Sugimoto?
He's apparently working
with an Ainu child
and he's got a few
tattooed skins.
This village is close to where
I met him before, so, seen him?
No, I haven't.
I see.
[TANIGAKI]
I can't stay here any longer.
Granny, I... I have to go.
I wish I could repay
you for everything.
[HUCI speaks Ainu]
[TANIGAKI gasps] Osoma!
Come on, tell her what I said!
Tell her I have no choice but
to leave now! Osoma, please!
[TANIGAKI]
Granny.
[speaking Ainu]
[gasps]
[OSOMA grunts]
Sinna kisar !
Get down, Osoma!
Don't move, okay?
[KOUHEI]
It seems we missed.
We probably should've just
killed him when we had
the chance, don't you think?
[OGATA] We would've had to
kill the witnesses, too.
I love my grandma.
Don't make me do that.
[OGATA]
Tankigaki's an honest man.
He wouldn't agree to do anything
to betray Lieutenant Tsurumi.
I made that clear
to Corporal Tamai.
[OGATA] Apparently, I didn't
make that clear enough.
My guess is, after they
failed to persuade him,
they tried to shut him up,
but he killed them instead.
Tanigaki must have planned
to wait until he was recovered,
then tell Lieutenant Tsurumi
that we betrayed him.
Just stay down, okay?
I have to fight, but...
...how'm I supposed to fight a
master marksman with no gun?
[OGATA] This Type 30 infantry
rifle is a good gun.
But it's difficult for your
average soldier to inflict a
fatal wound from a distance
of more than a hundred meters.
While that's not bad,
I can blow someone's head
off with perfect accuracy
within 300 meters.
The Seventh had a rough
time with the Russians.
They'd unleash their maxim guns
from the protection
of their bunkers.
If there was a unit of
precision marksmen like me,
many soldiers would
still be alive today.
I'm seeing movement in the
furthest window to the right.
He's using some kind of
claw to close the shades.
[TANIGAKI] From the way
they were talking today,
I think I can guess why
they want me dead.
[TAMAI] You see,
the thing to remember is,
the Seventh Division is just
a collection of strangers
from all over Japan. It's more
fragile than you might think.
And not everyone's interested
in Lieutenant Tsurumi's
grand ideals.
Then, are you saying that
there are people who intend
to betray him? Who are they?
Well, if that were to happen,
which side would
you find yourself on?
[TANIGAKI] So, he was talking
about Private Ogata.
I never imagined Corporal Tamai
would betray Tsurumi, too.
At this point, they're not with
the Seventh or anybody else.
They're just my enemies.
[SUGIMOTO] We were lucky
to find a place to sleep.
[SHIRAISHI] And we got
a little sake, to boot!
This is paradise!
[HIJIKATA] You guys don't
look like yanshuu to me.
[BOTH]
Huh?
You all on a trip?
[SUGIMOTO]
Yeah, sort of.
What a pretty little lady.
She looks about the same
age as my granddaughter.
Can I hold you for
a bit, little one?
She gets pretty grouchy
when she's sleepy.
[HIJIKATA]
Her eyes are a beautiful color.
If you look close, you can see
specks of green in the blue.
Perhaps there's some Russian
blood in your veins?
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
[SHIRAISHI] What the hell
is this old man doing?
I know someone with
the same kind of eyes.
Do you mind if I ask her name?
Asirpa.
Japanese name.
Beg your pardon?
She should have one
on her registration.
Well. I don't know,
I've never asked.
[HIJIKATA]
I see.
[SUGIMOTO]
Hm?
[HIJIKATA]
Hm. I'd better be on my way.
See you around, little Asirpa.
Make some copies.
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
That's a very weird old man.
That hit, for sure.
[OGATA] The way the
binoculars moved feels fake.
[KOUHEI] The central window.
He threw something out of it.
[KOUHEI] He's gonna use a
smokescreen to escape!
[OGATA]
He got the upper hand.
[KOUHEI grunts]
[TANIGAKI] I'm sorry for
putting a hole in your wall.
I'll come back and fix it.
[speaking Ainu]
Tanigaki Nispa, Asirpa told
me to hide this because
it would make Ryuu
feel better. So, I hid it.
Hold on. Is that?
Tetsuzou Nihei's rifle!
[OGATA]
He beat us.
But he can't possibly get
very far, as wounded as he is.
We'll just hunt him down.
[TANIGAKI]
I've only got a single round,
the last one Nihei ever loaded.
You made a mistake.
You didn't kill me
with that first shot.
And now you'll regret it.
♪
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "Fellow Traveler".