[NAGAKURA]
Twenty thousand kan .
[HIJIKATA] Yes, a thousand
times the amount
the other prisoners were told.
A mountain of treasure hidden
somewhere in Hokkaido,
just waiting to be found.
He and I shared a common goal.
So, though he lied to
the others, he told
me the true amount.
It's a third of the Japanese
governments' entire budget,
but if we get it out of the
country, it's worth much more.
I'm starting to think that
creating a new nation
isn't out of
my reach, after all.
♪
[USHIYAMA grunts]
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
[SHIRAISHI, SOLDIERS yell]
[USHIYAMA grunts]
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
What the...? What was that?
A hand grenade. It's an ambush.
[gunshots]
There! Shoot him!
[SHIRAISHI yelps]
Somebody save me!
[MAN A]
Ushiyama!
[USHIYAMA]
Hm?
What are you doing here?
Starting a fight with a
bunch of soldiers too.
All you were supposed to do was
wait in front of that brothel!
Shiraishi's right, screw you.
We're leaving. Let's go!
[KOUHEI gasps]
[SHIRAISHI yells]
[SOLDIER B] The explosions
came from up ahead.
Round up the soldiers,
and bring the horses, too.
Any idea what's going on?
I'm not sure, they might
be having a gunfight
over there or something.
[ALL shout]
[SHIRAISHI grunts] Seriously,
what the hell's goin' on?
[WOMEN scream]
[HIJIKATA]
Well?
[MAN D]
Looks like it worked!
[SOLDIER C] We shot this one,
and we're pursuing the other
two that escaped on horseback.
One more thing, sir.
We suspect one that fled
is a tattooed prisoner.
[TSURUMI] This one
has no tattoos at all.
So, was the tip-off a trap?
Did they simply want
to lure us out
so they could steal the
tattoos we already have?
Dynamite seems a bit much.
[SOLDIER B]
Lt. Tsurumi!
We looked into the
explosions we heard earlier.
They came from
Sakaimachi Street.
The finance district.
This entire thing was
just a diversion.
They're after the bank!
[MAN E]
We're outta here in one minute!
[NAGAKURA]
This is it, Hijikata.
[HIJIKATA]
Huh?
Over here. The tip
that we received.
It appears to have been correct.
Huh. This blunt old thing
doesn't feel right in my hand,
and I doubt it ever could.
After all this time,
it's mine once more!
[BRANCH MANAGER groans]
[TSURUMI] So, the branch
manager was threatened into
opening the vault, himself?
Fascinating. Then what
was the explosion for?
What's on the second floor?
[BRANCH MANAGER] Safe deposit
vaults for valuables,
but to get inside, you
need a key from both
the bank and the owner
of the vault, and they didn't
come up here, themselves, so...
[TSURUMI]
These walls are thin.
The explosion must've been
an attempt to get inside from
the back. Looks like their
plan worked like a charm.
What'd they want so bad they
were willing to split up?
Mainly, what's in those vaults
are bonds and jewelry
and little things like that.
Also, some works of art,
like paintings and katanas
that the bank owns.
Katanas?
[BRANCH MANAGER]
Izuminokami Kanesada.
Toshizou Hijikata!
[HIJIKATA] So, that's the
soldier called Tsurumi, is it?
There's something about his
face that I like. Brave.
[TSURUMI] That bastard even
stole the horse I borrowed.
A remnant from the shogunate.
No, an evil spirit whose hatred
still lives on in this world.
[SHIRAISHI]
Hey, ladies, how's it going?
Sounds like you've
had a rough day.
You're the one who's looking
pretty rough right now.
Ha. Anyway, about the
favor I asked for.
You saw one. A man with
those tattoos, right?
[WOMAN A] Yeah. We swapped
his with a new one,
just like you said.
[SHIRAISHI] Thanks, little miss.
Buy yourself something nice.
[WOMAN 8A] Hey, what did
you want that for, anyway?
Because now, Retar will
be able to sniff him out
even if he tries to
hide under an outhouse.
You want to borrow Retar?
Yes, please! I've just gotta
make friends with that wolf!
[SUGIMOTO]
Tell the truth, now.
You just want to sell his pelt
for drinking money, don't you?
[SHIRAISHI]
Ah! No way!
Retar isn't mine.
I can't lend him to you.
And besides, I'm never
getting close to Retar again.
I don't want the wolves
involved with this.
I don't know what it is
you've got planned,
but leave them out of it.
Hey, what's that?
There's something soft there.
Yes! Good job!
Now, spin the fur-twister
till it stops rotating
and pull it out!
Got it!
Oh, gosh! Look how cute it is!
[ASIRPA] Ooo, it's nice
and plump, too!
[SUGIMOTO] Shiraishi, grab it!
It's gonna fall off!
It's not moving, though.
Don't you think
it's prob'ly dead?
Tanuki are known to play dead.
Be careful, Shiraishi.
Don't let it get ahold
of your head. I mean it!
It's gonna try to
bite your head!
[SHIRAISHI]
Ow!
It's getting away!
[BOTH gasp]
[SUGIMOTO]
Why? Why're you so useless?
He's right, you really are.
[SUGIMOTO, ASIRPA]
Huh?
Ryuu! So, you followed us, huh?
Good boy, that's a good boy.
Tetsuzou Nihei trained you well!
Good boy. Nope, nope.
Don't bite me.
Okay, take a whiff, Ryuu.
This is the scent.
Time to go find this smell!
Just you wait. You're never
gonna call me useless again.
[RYUU whines]
[SHIRAISHI]
What's wrong?
[USHIYAMA grunts]
That's a job well done, Ryuu.
This is exactly who
we needed to find.
[SUGIMOTO, ASIRPA gasp]
[NAGAKURA] Another body was
found on the Shakotan coast.
The head was split
open with an axe.
And the one before that had
his throat slit with a blade.
The victim was apparently
just a herring fisherman.
Do we know if it was that man?
Yes, Kazuo Henmi.
A murderer with over a hundred
victims who's wandered
the whole length and
breadth of Japan.
I've heard him boasting
about it many times.
He's always bragged that the
trick to not being caught
is to keep moving and
never stay in one place.
A guy like Tetsuzou
Nihei is a hassle,
but predicting Kazuo Henmi's
actions is impossible.
[gasps]
Shh!
[USHIYAMA]
As for the rest.
[gasps]
[SHIRAISHI]
Stupid mutt!
[SHIRAISHI shouts]
You escape by
dislocating your joints?
[SHIRAISHI] I swear,
I'll skewer your eyeball!
[USHIYAMA grunts]
[SHIRAISHI groans]
No fair using
weapons now, Shiraishi.
[gasps]
[HIJIKATA]
Don't kill him, Ushiyama.
[USHIYAMA]
Hm?
[gasps]
I'm actually amazed you
found this place, Shiraishi.
Toshizou Hijikata!
[USHIYAMA] I know he looks
like an idiot, but I warn you,
don't underestimate him.
What will you do, Shiraishi?
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
[USHIYAMA] We're willing to
keep you alive, for right now.
Long as you let us
copy your tattoo.
The old man and me
are working together.
Did you seriously plan on
fighting the Seventh Division
all by yourself?
[HIJIKATA] You're not really
working alone, are you?
There's also a man called
the Immortal Sugimoto.
Immortal Sugimoto?
Now, there's an
interesting nickname.
Is this man your partner?
Well. Actually, it's a bit
more like he works for me.
He's strong, but he's
a super moody guy.
And he doesn't trust us
prisoners one bit.
There's no need for you to
tell him anything about us.
Just make sure that you make
good use of your bodyguard.
[HIJIKATA]
By the way.
[SHIRAISHI]
Mm?
Do you and this
"Immortal" Sugimoto
have even one of the
tattoos we're looking for?
No, we don't!
[HIJIKATA] Choose right now
whether we fight each other,
or work together.
[SHIRAISHI] The thing is,
I'm a pacifist.
[HIJIKATA] Then maybe
a good place to start,
would be with the skin
of Kazuo Henmi.
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
[SUGIMOTO]
The yanshuu ?
[SHIRAISHI]
Seasonal laborers.
They're hired to
fish for herring.
This time of year, people
migrate in from all over.
Perfect place for an escaped
convict to hide, right?
Lately, though,
some of the yanshuu
have been turning up dead.
The killer is a man named Henmi.
How do you know that?
[SHIRAISHI] Because the same
character was found carved
into all the dead
bodies' backs.
Their backs?
I've heard it said
that killing comes
as naturally as
breathing to him.
He looks like a normal man,
but he's just not.
[HENMI] There was a time I
had a brother, but one day...
...he was eaten by a boar on
the mountain near our home.
[HENMI]
All I did was hide and watch
while he cried and screamed.
I just sat there and
watched him suffer.
When I think about how
he struggled so hard,
how he was killed so
horribly by that monster,
even though he
fought and fought...
A monster he couldn't
bargain with.
When I think of how much
fear and pain he felt.
How the light faded from his
eyes as he gave in to despair.
When I remember those eyes,
It makes me want to kill
anyone and everyone I see.
[SHIRAISHI] His tattoo had the
character for "eye" in it.
[SUGIMOTO]
Makes sense. What a story.
I'm worried that prisoner
might go after my uncle.
Why?
He's on the coast
with the other men.
They're trying to
catch the whales
that are following the herring.
A whale hunt?
Sugimoto, let's go.
Off to the coast!
[SUGIMOTO]
Whatever you say.
So, this prisoner, Henmi.
You mentioned he had
no interest in the gold.
[SHIRAISHI]
Right.
That doesn't make sense.
He's been so cautious in order
to avoid being arrested.
So, why would he then
leave clues that are
meant to lure out
other prisoners?
I don't even want
to think about
what's going on in Henmi's head.
[SUGIMOTO]
Well, bright side:
if he's that bad a guy,
I won't feel as bad about
stripping off his skin.
[ALL cheer]
[SHIRAISHI] There are some
pretty large herring
fishing zones just
off the coast.
When they bring the
fish back to land,
they process them right there.
I wouldn't be
surprised if Henmi's
trying to blend in
with the workers.
[MAKANAKKURU]
Asirpa!
Achapo !
[MAKANAKKURU] Oh! Great timing!
Hurry, this way! Follow me!
[ALL]
Huh?
[MAKANAKKURU]
Row harder, Sugimoto!
Put your back into it!
Why are we doing this, again?
Another kotan ' s boat found a
whale and hit it with a harpoon,
but the whale's been
dragging them along the coast
ever since yesterday!
Sugimoto, let's help.
[ASIRPA]
That's the boat! We found them!
Look there! A humpe !
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
Try to aim for the neck!
The skin in that area's softer!
[SUGIMOTO]
Yeah, but where's the neck?
Yes! I got it!
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
[MAKANAKKURU]
Hang on tight
and don't get knocked
outta the boat!
Even this time of year,
the sea is plenty cold
enough to kill you!
[FISHERMEN chanting]
[SHIRAISHI] Oh, boy! The whale!
It's heading straight for them!
Hey, listen, it's going to
ram you guys! Be careful!
[FISHERMAN A] Hey, I think
that kid might be trying
to tell us something.
[HENMI]
Huh?
[FISHERMEN shout]
[HENMI shouts]
One fell in!
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
[FISHERMAN B]
Grab on! You can do it!
Let's help!
Quick! That ship's too big to
get back to the coast in time.
He needs to be fireside soon
or he'll die of hypothermia!
Got it! I'll cut the nets!
Shiraishi! It's up to you!
Bring us back
some whale, alright?
[SHIRAISHI]
Wh-What? H-Hold on!
[SHIRAISHI yells]
[SUGIMOTO]
Hang on!
We've got ya!
[MAKANAKKURU]
Let's hurry!
There should be fires on the
coast to help process the fish
once they're caught!
[HENMI]
Thank you. Thank you.
I didn't want to die.
Not today. Not this way.
Not 'cause I fell in the sea.
That would've
been so boring!
[HENMI] It's so warm.
I've really been saved!
[SUGIMOTO] You should
warm your back, too.
And take off all
those wet clothes.
Uh. Take 'em off here?
[HENMI]
I'm sure that was Shiraishi
on the boat back there.
That soldier is
probably with him.
They must've taken
the bait I left,
and come to the coast in
search of a tattooed prisoner.
I'm, uh... I'm a little shy
about taking my clothes off
in front of strangers.
Huh? You're embarrassed?
[HENMI] Shit. That just
made him more suspicious.
[HENMI gasps]
Will this help?
[HENMI] He's nice! He's a
genuinely kind person.
Maybe I'm wrong. Maybe he
didn't come to kill a prisoner.
No... He has the same scent
as me. He reeks of it.
The scent of a killer.
I wonder if he'd be willing
to kill me in a horrible way.
Like that beast that ate
my brother years ago.
[HENMI sighs]
Maybe I should just show him.
[HENMI gasps] No, no.
I can't show him my tattoos.
That's basically suicide.
I need to be strong and struggle
hard with all my strength.
Just like my brother.
So, um. I'm already feeling a
lot better, thanks to you,
so I'm gonna go get some
dry clothes from the dorm.
[HENMI] I want to know more
about this guy. Who is he?
[MAN F coughs]
[HENMI]
Huh?
Those tattoos.
They aren't really somethin'
you see every day, huh?
Why are you here in
the middle of the day?
[coughs] My cold took a
bad turn, so I came to rest.
[gasps]
S'cuse me.
Yes...? Hello, again.
Sorry to bother you,
but are people other than
fishermen allowed
to stay here, too?
Do you think there'd be a way to
work off the price of lodging?
I'd be happy to ask my
boss for you later today.
[HENMI] The herring
is gutted immediately
at the fishing grounds, then it
goes through the drying process.
Herring rots, so it's how
we preserve the fish
to send it to the mainland. The
leftover parts of the fish are
stripped of their oil and used
as a high-quality fertilizer.
It's a very popular product.
Wow.
After they're squeezed
for oil, you end up with these
big blocks, which then
need to be chipped
into tiny parts so they can dry.
This is the knife that's used
to cut the blocks apart.
Look how long,
big and shiny it is.
I think it's incredibly
beautiful, don't you?
Go ahead, why don't
you try it out? Here!
[SUGIMOTO]
So, just slice it?
You look amazing!
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[gasps]
Did I do it right?
Sugimoto. We should
really go after Shiraishi.
[gasps]
[ASIRPA] We don't know what
our enemy's face looks like,
so there's no sense
in staying here.
[SUGIMOTO] Fair point.
You're right, let's go.
Um, not to butt in, but you
should stay and eat!
I feel like it's the
very least I can do
after you've saved my life!
There's some warm white rice.
White rice?
[SUGIMOTO] This looks great.
Oh, this herring is so good!
It's got just the right
kick to go with these
sweet pickled vegetables.
[ASIRPA] And white rice
is such a luxury!
This combination
is really hinna !
Hinna , hinna !
[HENMI chuckels]
[ASIRPA]
I'm off to osoma .
Aw, come on. Call it
a bathroom, okay?
Hey, by the way, you didn't
happen to be at Port Arthur,
did you? How was that?
How was what?
Did you have to kill anyone?
Well, yeah, it was a war.
Do you remember how
many people you killed?
I'll never forget their faces.
The ones I killed up close
enough to see, anyway.
[HENMI]
He's just like me.
[HENMI] Do you think
it's because of guilt
that you can't forget?
Remembering them
is my atonement.
The least I can do.
I had no choice.
I was a soldier
and it was my duty.
In exchange, when my
time does come,
I don't think for a second
that I'm gonna go peacefully.
[HENMI] Mmm. I want him
to kill me so bad.
It's settled,
I'll try to kill him.
Because if he's really what
I've been seeking all this time,
then there's no way somebody
like me could kill him, anyway!
♪
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "Gleaming".