[SHIRAISHI] That's the seventh
division's headquarters.
The windows are barred,
and they've got men standing
guard all night,
at every entrance.
We can try a rescue, but it
might already be too late.
Even Immortal Sugimoto's luck
has to run out sometime.
No, Sugimoto is
still alive. I know it.
His strength comes from
having a fearless heart.
I've only known one other
man who would jump
into a bear's den:.
My father.
Sugimoto has befriended
the Grim Reaper.
He doesn't fear death.
That's how he survives.
That's what makes him:
Immortal Sugimoto.
♪
[SUGIMOTO groans]
[YOUHEI grunts]
[grunting]
Hey, knock it off!
You were told not
to kill him yet!
I'm gonna chop him up and feed
the pieces to the damn pigs!
You're lucky your friends
showed up when they did!
Otherwise you and your brother
would be dead on the floor!
Let's keep those twins away
from Sugimoto from now on.
Sir.
Think you coulda
been any slower?
I was making all that
noise for a reason.
Where the hell were you?
[SOLDIER C]
This guy's crazy in the head.
He's a tough one.
[ASIRPA]
Hm?
Sugimoto's in there
and he's alive!
[sighs]
[SHIRAISHI] He's tied
up real good, though.
I'm guessing that means
he's hidden the tattoos
someplace else.
See those old bars.
They're pretty rusty.
If we can get one of them off,
I can dislocate my
joints and sneak in.
Kid, I like to gamble,
and I'm willing to bet on you.
All you gotta do is promise
me a share of the gold,
and I'll do what I can to
help you save Sugimoto.
It's a deal. I'm not interested
in the gold, anyway.
If you find it, you can
split it with Sugimoto.
Great. Sounds like
a bargain to me.
So, here's the plan:
We're gonna tie the rope to
one of these horses out here.
On my signal, startle the
horse and it'll run
and rip off the frame,
then we'll make our escape.
You got any soap? That'll help
me wriggle through the bars.
Huh... How about fat?
[SHIRAISHI]
Huh?
[ASIRPA]
I've got bear fat.
[SUGIMOTO]
I gotta get outta here.
The twins will be back.
And next time,
they're gonna kill me.
--[squishing]
--[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[SHIRAISHI]
Ah... Just droppin' in.
A ghost?
Shiraishi, the Escape King!
What the hell're
you doing here?
A scary Ainu girl threatened
me with a poison arrow
if I didn't come.
[SUGIMOTO sighs]
Asirpa.
[horse whines]
What's that racket?
Sounds like the
horses got spooked.
It's a horse thief!
That's not going to be good.
The horses must have
picked up your scent.
Oh, great.
That's not good at all.
Look, just get these
cuffs off, okay?
[BOTH gasp]
[YOUHEI] Go keep watch, Kouhei.
No one gets in, got it?
If I take off his cuffs
after I kill him,
we can just tell everyone
he died trying to escape.
Hold on, first,
give me your gun.
A shot'll bring
everyone running.
Just use the bayonet.
Huh?
[YOUHEI groans]
Toothless asshole.
I knew it was you!
[wet thud]
[KOUHEI yells]
He was like this when
we opened the door.
I'm not sure what happened, sir.
[yelling continues]
[SUGIMOTO groans]
Look at his guts.
He won't last the night.
Well, it seems the
candle of your life
is getting dimmer
by the second.
[SUGIMOTO]
Save me.
I'll give you the tattoos or
anything else you want.
Prepare the sled!
Deliver Sugimoto to the
finest hospital in the city!
Wake up a doctor and have
him treated immediately!
Even if you have to put
a gun to someone's head.
[TSURUMI]
Wait. We'll do our best.
You make sure to remember that.
If you feel the cold hand
of death closing in,
you'd better tell us where
the tattoos are. You got it?
Do you know what
"immortal" means?
I will need to see
to things here.
Keep talking to him
along the way, understood?
Find out where they
are before he dies.
Yes, sir!
Something's strange. What is it?
A deep wound on the right hand.
Where did he get that?
Did it happen while he was
defending himself, or...?
[TSURUMI sniffs] His left
hand is perfectly fine,
yet he didn't switch?
Tell me, did you really die
fighting Sugimoto like this,
you clumsy bastard? Answer me!
Or did he plant this
in a corpse's hand?
Hm? What the hell is this?
Why are there bloody
fingerprints on the inside
of his belt?
[SOLDIER H gasps]
So, why would you redress a
man you'd already killed?
[SOLDIER H grunts]
[TSURUMI gasps]
What's going on back--
[TSURUMI]
Crafty bastard stole his guts!
[SOLDIER I grunts]
C'mon, go! Run faster!
[gasps]
[horse whines]
Another time, Immortal.
What happened here?
How'd the horse go down?
I didn't hear any gunshots.
[TSURUMI] Hm? Where could
this wound have come from?
You can eat later.
This meat has poison in it.
[SOLDIER J] Lieutenant,
someone started a fire!
Stay back, sir!
It's gonna set off the ammo!
That settles it.
From now on, we're going to
let Sugimoto and his people
gather the tattoos for us.
They're quite obviously
better at it than we are.
Apologies, sir.
The fire spread so fast
we weren't able to get
the tattoo out in time!
I've kept it safe!
Not comfortably, though.
This thing doesn't breathe!
[SHIRAISHI] Well, that explains
why I couldn't find it.
What a psycho.
I'm so sorry. When I left,
it was due to pride.
Now, you've saved me.
I'm ashamed.
[SUGIMOTO yells]
Ow!
[NAGAKURA]
Here's some money for now,
as well as some of the very
latest weapons from the west.
I'm afraid it's all I'm able to
offer you for the time being.
It's enough. Thank you for this.
[NAGAKURA] If only I wasn't
so slow and stiff these days.
I've gotten too old to run
alongside you anymore.
I know you're lying.
How many years of your life did
you devote to the Shinsengumi?
Don't tell me you're
not excited, Nagakura.
[USHIYAMA]
Nagakura?
Could this grizzled antiquity
really be the Shinsengumi's
finest swordsman,
Shinpachi Nagakura?
[USHIYAMA] Hey, you old
Shinsengumi geezers.
Tell the truth. You're not
just after the gold, are you?
[SHIRAISHI] So, what should
we do with this horse?
That is a good question.
We can't just leave it here.
I mean, would you look
at this guy? He likes me!
No, no, no, we have
to get rid of it.
Stands out like a sore thumb.
And Retar deserves a reward.
[SUGIMOTO groans]
Then it's settled.
[SHIRAISHI] Alright! Horse meat!
Who's up for sakuranabe ?
Sakuranabe ? What's that?
It's just horse meat
prepared like sukiyaki.
Very popular dish in Tokyo.
So, sukiyaki. Is it good?
It's the best!
But we're gonna need an egg
to really make it properly.
I'll go hit up
the local farmers!
Back in a bit!
[SUGIMOTO]
This is awkward.
Uh...
I noticed, they really
ripped up your face, huh?
You're probably
covered in wounds.
You should rest.
Asirpa.
This is what it's going to
be like, searching for the gold.
If something were to happen
to you, I don't know how I'd
face your grandmother and
the rest of the village.
What you're saying is that
I'm slowing you down.
No, that's not what I meant.
What's this?
Put it on your face.
I've heard that horse meat can
help reduce swelling, so...
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[ASIRPA] Sugimoto, I've already
seen my father brutally killed.
I know this is dangerous.
But I've chosen to go, and it
was completely my decision.
I made it in order to achieve
my goals and forge my own path.
The one who treated
me like a child,
didn't trust me as
a partner, acted alone,
made dumb choices,
and was caught.
That was you.
[SHIRAISHI] Look, I got burdock,
cabbage, and the eggs.
Plus, they gave us sugar,
soy sauce, and saké!
Great. Thank you.
[SHIRAISHI]
What's going on here?
Did someone's dog just die?
C'mon, we're about to
have a great meal!
Hey, I'm not lookin' to get
involved in some kinda
couple's quarrel,
so let's eat some stew.
You two can make up later. Eh?
Once the meat's the color of
cherry blossoms, it's ready.
Mix it with the egg, and then...
[SUGIMOTO]
Ready to eat.
It's great! Seriously, amazing!
So good! The horsemeat
is nice and mild,
so the miso flavor
really comes through.
We're lucky you had
that miso paste!
Wait. Is there osoma in this?
Huh? Osoma ?
[SUGIMOTO groans]
Look, Asirpa, I'm sorry,
but proper sakuranabe
needs miso!
[ASIRPA groans]
[SHIRAISHI]
Uh-oh, she's not a fan of miso?
[SUGIMOTO] She's convinced
herself it's actually poop.
[SHIRAISHI]
Really? Huh.
The Japanese and the Ainu
sure have culture gaps
in some unexpected places.
[SUGIMOTO]
Hey, I'm sorry.
There's plenty of
meat left over.
I'll remake it for you.
[gasps]
[ASIRPA gags]
She's gonna do it!
[ASIRPA groans]
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[ASIRPA]
Huh...? Osoma is yummy!
Oh, I'm so proud
I could just cry!
I don't know what
just happened,
but I'm guessing
you liked it.
Hinna , hinna !
Hinna is right!
[ASIRPA]
More poop, please!
[SHIRAISHI]
Sure, eat up!
[SUGIMOTO]
I'm so happy!
The man we're about to meet,
Zenjirou Shibukawa,
has his own gang of bandits.
I assume your plan is
to bring him and his men
over to your side.
[HIJIKATA] I sent a messenger,
but he didn't come back.
So you're busting your way in?
There are more of them
than there are of us.
Numbers don't make a difference
to us and they never have.
The only people who are worth
a damn in this world are
the ones who are willing
to lay down their lives.
[HIJIKATA] If you want to live,
then prepare to die!
[MEN]
Huh?
[MAN B] Hey! Who the hell said
you could just walk in here?
How cute of you to try!
Back off! Up you go!
Shibukawa. My messenger...
I trust he spoke with you?
Yeah, I beat the living hell
out of him till he squealed.
Told me about the treasure.
It's all very fascinating.
Why don't you show
me your tattoos?
Not yet.
[HIJIKATA]
These are the heads of your men
who were on guard outside.
So, do we help each
other or kill each other?
I'll leave it to you.
[sighs]
You win, friend.
Kill them, now!
[yelling, grunting]
Slaughter them all!
No one's leaving here alive!
[USHIYAMA]
The demon.
Former Vice-Commander
of the Shinsengumi.
[USHIYAMA] The saying goes
that if a man doesn't die
when he should, he faces a
shame even greater than death.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing,
starting a war at our age?
It's sheer madness,
and you know it.
Hijikata, you wouldn't be
looking for a reason
to die now, would you?
I plan to live for
another century.
Don't worry, my friend.
[USHIYAMA]
Old man,
you really planning on making
a new Shinsengumi?
Sorry to disappoint, but I'm
only in this thing for the gold.
You have to know taking over
Hokkaido is nothing more
than a fantasy.
There are many
who long to make
the fantasy of Ezo's
independence a reality.
They've dreamed
of it for generations.
Perhaps now is their time.
Where did the Scat King go?
Shiraishi went into town
to gather up some info.
It's probably best if I stay
away from there for a while.
[ASIRPA] Sugimoto, look!
Ezo deer tracks.
They're still fresh.
Right! You ready to track?
Let's do it.
Are Ezo deer good?
[ASIRPA] The brains are pretty
tasty if you add a little salt.
You're moving way too slow.
We'll never catch this deer.
Just gimme a minute, okay?
I'm so tired.
Man, I need water.
Sad little Sisam .
[ASIRPA] You're in luck,
look what we have here.
Sarunashi vines.
These suck up tons of water.
[ASIRPA] If you cut them,
the sap comes pouring out.
We use these when we run out
of water in the mountains.
Uh... Hey, hey, could I?
Give me some.
Don't drink it all!
How're you so strong?
There are lots of good
uses for sarunashi vines.
Look, they're even sturdy enough
to make snowshoes out of, see?
That's much better!
[SUGIMOTO]
What is it?
Look, Sugimoto. A buck
sharpened his antlers here.
He did that to
mark his territory.
If we're noisy and hit
this tree with a stick,
he might come back to defend it.
You use that thing
way too much!
Huci told me that there used to
be a lot more deer in this area.
They were easy to catch.
[ASIRPA]
Deer aren't treated as gods.
They were called " yuk ,"
which means " prey ,"
because they were easily caught.
It was said that yuk were
scattered across the world by
the gods to be food for humans.
[ASIRPA] But one winter,
the snow fell so heavily
the deer weren't able
to find enough food.
Many of them starved to death.
We believed that someone
must've treated the deer poorly.
And so, it was said that the
gods got angry and stopped
sending them for us.
Interesting.
[SUGIMOTO]
It actually showed up.
It's as big as a horse!
[ASIRPA]
Go slow and silent.
I missed the vitals!
I know. Chase it!
[ASIRPA]
Look for blood on the leaves.
Find the tracks where
it left the thicket.
[SUGIMOTO] Damn it.
Why didn't I take my time?
Now all I've done is make the
poor thing suffer needlessly.
I have to finish it
for its own sake.
This looks like one
dog and two men.
One of the men is big,
with a strange gait.
An injured right leg, maybe?
Not him...
[TETSUZOU] Comparing the brown
bears of Hokkaido to the black
bears Tohoku Matagi hunt is
like comparing wolves to pups.
This breed here has been raised
by the Ainu for generations.
It doesn't fear brown bears.
A Murata rifle. Hard to use,
and it only holds one bullet.
That thing's obsolete.
Why arm yourself with a relic?
[TETSUZOU grunts] Yeah, the guns
that you soldiers use
all hold five rounds,
isn't that right?
Nice and convenient.
Okay, Ryuu. Go!
Get that bear out in the open.
[RYUU barks]
Don't intervene. This fight's
between me and the bear.
Hey, where're your
other bullets?
I thought hunters who used
Murata guns held extra bullets
between their fingers.
[TETSUZOU]
If you have five bullets,
you think you get five chances.
With one shot, you do
it right the first time.
[TANIGAKI] He's standing his
ground against a charging bear?
He must be insane!
[TETSUZOU]
You get scared, you lose.
Well, Tanigaki Matagi,
are you still planning
to follow me, or what?
I didn't save you from the cold
because I wanted a lover.
You seek the white wolf, too.
Isn't that right?
I heard something once
from a medicine-seller
back in my homeland.
He told me about a
bear-hunter in Hokkaido.
"Send that man up
a mountain," he said,
"and all the bears on it
will start disappearing."
[TANIGAKI] The name he gave
me was yours. Tetsuzou Nihei.
♪
[NARRATOR]
Next time:. "Hunter's Soul".