[TANIGAKI pants]
[TANIGAKI] No prey can escape
without leaving tracks.
There's always something.
Springtime in the mountains
means there's still snow.
Gives the pursuer an advantage.
I found quite a few tracks.
Do you think this
bastard really is hurt?
Whether he's hurt
or not, he's a Matagi.
He knows very well how
to move on a mountain.
[TANIGAKI pants]
[TANIGAKI] At least I don't
think they saw my gun.
That means they're confident
they won't be shot.
Maybe I should set up
an ambush for them.
[TANIGAKI]
If I take down Private Ogata,
will Nikaidou leave? Nah.
I don't think he's that soft.
[TANIGAKI]
I've only got one bullet.
Keep running and keep thinking.
[TANIGAKI grunts]
[TANIGAKI] But how much
distance can I put
between us with this leg?
[gasps]
[TANIGAKI]
Bear tracks.
The cub is walking in
its mother's footsteps.
[grunts]
♪
[KOUHEI] I think we've
completely lost him.
Great. The sun will
go down pretty soon.
It doesn't matter to me what
Tanigaki's planning to tell
Lieutenant Tsurumi.
I don't give two shits about
that gold. I just want to kill
Saichi Sugimoto as soon
as I goddamn can!
[TANIGAKI] Did whatever leave
these tracks bury this?
It's a greedy one.
My guess is that it's
patrolling this area daily.
Waiting to recover
from hibernation.
Judging by the way
the snow melts,
it comes in the morning.
Do you think I
could start a fire?
Not without signaling
where we are.
You want him to be able
to attack us in the dark?
Fine by me.
Then at least we won't have
to track him any more!
I'm sick of freezing my
ass off in Hokkaido,
sick of the military, all of it!
I want to go back
home to Shizuoka!
[OGATA]
Smoke from a fire.
Maybe another hunter?
Tanigaki wouldn't start a fire.
Let's get a little closer.
Go take a look.
If those are Tanigaki's tracks,
give me a signal.
[KOUHEI gasps]
Great, so I'm bait now.
I'll be here, backing you up.
It's a hundred meters, at most.
No matter who it is,
I won't miss.
There's just one set of tracks.
Definitely Tanigaki.
Was that idiot really eating a
damn deer instead of running?
[OGATA] It's a trap, for sure.
What's he planning?
[TANIGAKI]
Where are you... Private Ogata?
[KOUHEI sighs]
So warm.
I'm hungry. Maybe I'll
have some, too.
Wait a second.
How'd Tanigaki manage to
kill this thing, anyway?
[bear roars]
There!
I knew it was a trap.
[groans]
[roars]
[KOUHEI]
You bastard!
[TANIGAKI] What's wrong, Ogata?
You're not even gonna help him?
[OGATA] So, that's what
Tanigaki's doing.
That means he'll be waiting
for me to make a move.
If I shoot, he'll see
the gun smoke.
Shoot the
goddamned thing, Ogata!
[TANIGAKI]
Shoot!
[KOUHEI screams]
Ogata!
[KOUHEI groans]
[OGATA]
Okay. I'm right here, Tanigaki.
How do you plan to
fight me without a gun?
Throw rocks at me?
Hard on.
[MISHIMA]
Don't move, Tanigaki!
I know that voice. Mishima!
What the hell are
you doing here?
[MISHIMA] Private Ogata
and Nikaidou were being
tracked this entire time.
Their locations were being
reported to Lieutenant Tsusumi.
[MISHIMA] Tsurumi let them go
because he was hopeful that
their presence might smoke
out the other rebels.
I wasn't planning to
do anything until Private Ogata
made contact with
Corporal Tamai's group.
But, you took care
of them already.
Yeah, but...
[MISHIMA]
I know. You didn't betray us.
That's why they came after you.
Tsurumi and the others are
actually nearby. Let's go.
Then you can talk to
the Lieutenant yourself.
Mishima. I don't know.
Tanigaki, what's wrong?
[TANIGAKI grunts]
[MISHIMA groans]
[TANIGAKI] Shit!
That bastard is still alive?
[OGATA coughs]
[TANIGAKI]
Private Ogata!
[OGATA]
Was that Mishima?
I thought I was careful
not to be followed.
In that case,
I need to end Tanigaki
before Tsurumi gets here.
[gasps]
[TSURUMI] All I ask is:
don't shoot him in the head.
[OGATA] Well, that was fast.
I can see why his
superior officers were
so terrified of the man.
It's Mishima!
We know what the
gunfire was, now.
It was between
Mishima and Ogata,
once Ogata discovered that
he was being followed.
It looks as though
Nikaidou is still alive.
Fine, fine. Now you can shoot
the other one in the head.
[HAJIME]
Advance!
[groans]
Dammit! He's avoiding
shooting the vitals
to slow us down!
He ran north! Follow him!
I should be in the clear.
With Tsurumi's men on his tail,
he'll have no reason
to follow me.
It pains me to tell you this,
but you don't look
good with one ear.
Attractiveness is all
about symmetry, you know.
The Shinsengumi would
make you commit seppuku
the minute you fled.
Then there's the
Ainu punishment,
which involves removing the ears
and nose and banishing you,
The Seventh enjoys the
best of both worlds,
we'll chop off your
ears and nose,
then have you commit seppuku.
So, why don't you tell me
who else is betraying us?
I want their names, Nikaidou.
Now!
[grunts]
This offensive protrusion right
here is the nose of a traitor.
It's no wonder I don't
care for the shape of it.
How 'bout we play pin the tail
on the donkey with your face!
Well, I truly hope you all have
a good time, Lieutenant Tsusumi.
Enjoy your little game.
What if I offer to let you
kill Sugimoto, Private?
[KOUHEI gasps]
Komiya was in on it, too!
[KOMIYA gasps] Wait! He's lying!
I'm not a traitor!
It's the nose.
I see a trend, here!
[KOMIYA screams]
I guess I'll see you on the
other side, Lieutenant Tsurumi.
[KOMIYA screams]
[KOUHEI]
Saichi sugimoto...
[SUGIMOTO] We've got
five tattoos, total, now.
Maybe Lieutenant Tsurumi only
has the one that Shiraishi saw?
[SHIRAISHI] I'm not sure,
it's hard to say.
Well, who else is
after the tattoos?
That one guy you were
talking about? Hijikata?
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
He's been actively recruiting
the other prisoners, too.
If we find him, chances are,
we'll find a lot of tattoos.
Toshizou Hijikata.
What's that guy like, I wonder?
[SHIRAISHI] He was right in
front of you not long ago.
He has a way about him
that makes it impossible
to believe that he's over 70.
In fact, the other prisoners
used to say he must've eaten
mermaid flesh.
Mermaid?
It's a monster with the torso of
a man and a bottom like a fish.
If a human eats their flesh,
it's said they receive endless
youth and eternal life.
Yeah, there's that old
legend called "Yaobikuni".
A girl who eats mermaid flesh
then becomes forever young.
But she lives so long,
she can only watch as
everyone she loves dies.
She lives for centuries
before finally becoming a nun
and retreating from the
world to live in a cave.
Oh, the pain of not being
able to die when you should.
[sighs]
You know, if I was immortal,
I wouldn't care about the gold.
Hey, look!
Check it out, Sugimoto! It's a
perfect little Adonis flower!
It's so adorable.
Spring's on its way, huh?
[ASIRPA]
Cirai appapo .
We call this bright little
guy the huchen flower.
[SUGIMOTO]
Huchen ? You mean like the fish?
[ASIRPA] Yup. The huchen
appear in the spring.
The blooming of the
cirai appapo is a sign
they're coming up
the river soon.
[SHIRAISHI]
Huh? The river's been damned.
[ASIRPA] It's one of the
ways the Ainu catch fish.
[SHIRAISHI]
I've heard that huchen are
actually pretty tasty. Think we
could catch some around here?
[ASIRPA]
It's not that easy.
You run the risk of finding an
Iwan Onnechep Kamuy .
What the hell is that?
[ASIRPA] Once, there was a
hunter being chased by a bear
who tried to escape
across Shikaribetsu Lake.
After a while the bear vanished,
so he went to see what happened
and he saw a huge huchen
with the bear's front leg
sticking out of its mouth.
Iwan Onnechep Kamuy ,
greatest of all huchen .
Ah... The greatest, huh?
[SHIRAISHI] It's surprisingly
deep, you guys! Help me!
It's cold!
[SUGIMOTO] What are you doing?
Here, grab on, you idiot!
Iwan Onnechep Kamuy !
That fish ate Shiraishi!
Shiraishi...
[SUGIMOTO]
Shiraishi!
[ASIRPA, SUGIMOTO gasp]
[SUGIMOTO]
Look a mermaid.
[ASIRPA gasps]
Kiroranke Nispa!
That you, Asirpa?
Wait, you know this guy?
Sure I do. He's an old
friend of my father's.
I finally found you,
and it's about time.
[ASIRPA]
Huh?
Look at all this great skin.
You could make a whole
suit of clothes with it!
Wait, fish-skin clothes?
[ASIRPA]
Sure, it's called cepur .
It keeps the wind and rain out.
You can also use it to make
boots or a sheath for a dagger.
Well, that's very
useful information.
Thanks for that.
But also, the skin is
seriously delicious.
Makes it hard to decide whether
we should use it or just eat it.
Ah... It's a real
dilemma every time.
You know my vote.
[ASIRPA, SUGIMOTO giggle]
The skin's so thick, but then
it gets nice and soft
when you cook it!
Hinna , hinna !
It's a pretty great day when
you eat a legendary giant fish.
Sugimoto, the eyeballs
are like boiled octopus.
You open wide and suck.
It's so big.
Sugimoto. Immortal Sugimoto?
[ALL]
Hm?
Where'd you hear that?
Well, I'm with the
Seventh Division.
[ASIRPA, SHIRAISHI gasp]
You work for
Lieutenant Tsurumi?
[KIRORANKE]
Mm?
Wait, Sugimoto.
Lieutenant Tsurumi?
My platoon was commanded
by a different lieutenant.
And I've had nothing
to do with them.
Not since I left the army.
Well, I suppose there
were twenty thousand men
in the Seventh. I guess not
everybody works for Tsurumi.
I recognized the name
and the facial wound.
Didn't think I'd be seeing a
hero from the war way out here.
A hero? All I did was not die.
Tell me, Asirpa,
why is it you're hanging
around with these men?
He's my partner. But Shiraishi
here is basically useless.
[SHIRAISHI]
Mm-hm.
Alright, then. If you say
they can both be trusted,
then I believe you.
Listen, Asirpa.
There's something important
that I need to tell you.
[ASIRPA gasps]
[KIRORANKE] An old Japanese
man came to my village.
He said he was looking
for a particular woman.
Asuko Kochoube.
Oh, no! But how does he know
that name? My Japanese name!
My mom and dad are the
only ones who knew it,
and they're both dead!
[SUGIMOTO]
Asirpa's Japanese name?
[HIJIKATA]
Do you mind if I ask her name?
I already knew everything
about what happened
at the Abashiri Prison.
Nopperabo gave the prisoners a
hint so that they could make
contact with his friends
who were on the outside.
"Asuko Kochoube in Otaru".
Nopperabo was trying to
entrust the gold to Asirpa.
[SUGIMOTO]
Hm...
Wait a minute, are you saying?
[KIRORANKE]
Nopperabo. is Asirpa's father.
[gasps]
Impossible! Aca ...
He can't be the one
who stole the Ainu's
gold and killed them!
[grunts]
Okay, tell me, how do you
know Asirpa's Japanese name?
It's because I came to Japan
with Asirpa's father.
[HIJIKATA] You see, Nopperabo
isn't an Ainu from Japan.
Judging purely from the
route he ended up taking
after stealing the gold,
he was trying his best
to take it through Otaru, and
eventually, out of the country.
And all this time, I thought,
if we finally found the gold,
Nopperabo would die and
Asirpa would have her revenge.
[ASIRPA] I won't believe it.
Not until I see it for myself.
I'm going to
meet Nopperabo, in person.
If all of this is true and
he really is my father,
then I think he should
be willing to tell his
daughter everything.
Truth be told,
i'm sure that'll be easier
than finding the prisoners
who are scattered
all around Hokkaido.
At least you know
exactly where he is.
[SHIRAISHI whistles]
Hey, now, it ain't that easy.
Take it from me, I've escaped
from prisons all over Japan.
Abashiri is by far the
worst of the whole lot.
It's not like you can just walk
in and sit him down for a chat.
[ASIRPA gasps]
Not unless you have
the help of this guy!
Scat King. Oh, wait,
I mean Escape King!
[SUGIMOTO]
Hm.
An Escape King?
What is that about?
Actually. Shiraishi is one
of the tattooed prisoners
who escaped Abashiri.
Really? He's one of them?
You wanna show him?
[SHIRAISHI]
Uh...
Wouldja look at that. Aren't you
supposed to skin them?
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
Deduced that pretty quick, huh?
Only he could've done this.
This is him all over.
Do you have any more?
[SUGIMOTO]
No.
[KIRORANKE] Alright, then.
As someone who came
from the same
land as Nopperabo,
I will take responsibility
for stealing the gold
and harming the Ainu.
I don't care if you take a
fair share for yourselves,
but the rest must be
returned to those people.
That is what I want to
happen at the end of this.
[music plays]
[ALL]
Huh?
[SHIRAISHI]
What the... Tanigaki?
My uniform stands out, so I
started wearing an attus .
Surprisingly comfortable.
[KIRORANKE]
That tonkori. I remember it.
Asirpa's father got it back
when we were in Sakhalin.
Oh, wait. Aren't you...?
[TANIGAKI]
Hm?
Do you know this guy?
You're Asirpa's uncle,
aren't you?
[ALL gasp]
[OSOMA giggles]
So, you're heading to Abashiri?
Asahikawa perfectly
marks the halfway point
between here and there.
[TANIGAKI] It's also where
the Seventh is headquartered.
Here's an idea. What if we went
ahead and told the Seventh
all about Lieutenant Tsurumi?
The problem is
someone's already
working for him on the inside.
Lieutenant Colonel Yodogawa.
During the battle for
two-oh-three Hill,
Tsurumi pointed out the flaws
in his attack plan many times,
but the records were erased.
Ever since, Yodogawa's been
forced to do whatever
Tsurumi says.
Then there's really
no point, right?
Either way, we're going
to have a fight
on our hands somewhere.
Let's take this route.
What's there?
Sapporo. There's a
gunsmith I know there.
We can buy explosives and
weapons without being followed.
Explosives?
Oh, did I not say?
See, I used to be a sapper.
Back on hill two-oh-three,
I was known for making
improvised grenades,
which I then used to blow the
Russian's pillbox all to hell.
That's good to know.
And I'm very glad to hear it.
Shiraishi, why were you
in the girls' toilet?
[SHIRAISHI stutters] Listen,
Sugimoto, I've been thinking.
Are we sure about
taking this guy with us?
Hey, I don't trust you any
more than I trust him, okay?
[SHIRAISHI]
Oh...
It feels like he's
hiding something, though.
Something specific
about Nopperabo.
But if Asirpa likes him,
he can't be that bad of a guy.
The village needs
these horses,
so make sure you bring them
back by planting time.
Right.
Take care of Huci, okay?
[TANIGAKI]
Hm.
Is it just me or am
I on a baby horse?
[SUGIMOTO]
Let's go! First, to Sapporo...
...and then to Abashiri!
[SHIRAISHI] Seriously,
it feels really small!
♪
Sheesh, that was rough,
And how bizarre.
Seeing sleet and lightning
at this time of the year.
[IENAGA]
"Spring thunder," they call it.
Like a cannon signaling
the arrival of spring.
Please, come inside.
Happy to show you the way.
[NARRATOR]
Next Time:
"Everybody, Get Together!
It's a Murder Hotel!"