[SUGIMOTO]
Rabbit chitatap stew?
[ASIRPA]
With dried Ezo matsutake
and shimeji mushrooms.
And I've mixed dried alpine leek
into the meat for extra flavor.
Here we go.
[SUGIMOTO]
Mm! That's good!
The squirrel was a lot fattier.
This is perfect!
Ah! That hits the spot.
Nice and warm.
[gasps] You know what? This is
really delicious already,
but I think a little miso
might make it even better.
What is miso?
[SUGIMOTO]
Oh, you're in for a treat.
[gasps]
Sugimoto, That's osoma !
[SUGIMOTO]
Osoma ?
You eat poop!
Okay, it's not poop.
Don't be silly.
[ASIRPA]
No, that's poop!
I'm telling you, it's not!
Will you just try it, please?
[ASIRPA] Why are you
trying to feed me poop?
I refuse! Absolutely not!
[SUGIMOTO]
It's not poop.
Ah, yeah. Perfect.
Just as good as I
thought it would be.
I mean, if you're Japanese,
you gotta love miso.
That's great. This guys
willingly eating poop.
We're doomed.
You know, it's not
nice to shame people
for what they like to eat.
Hinna , hinna .
[ASIRPA]
Stop that!
♪
[ASIRPA] We'll find a bear
den just down this hill.
Most of the time, bears will
dig their own dens,
but they'll also reuse a
den if they can find one.
There's one right over there.
Go on, take a look.
Wait. Why should I go?
[ASIRPA] If there're
icicles on the entrance,
or it smells like raw meat,
there's likely a bear inside.
Be quiet when
you approach, Sugimoto.
[SUGIMOTO] It should
be hibernating, right?
[ASIRPA] It's just half-asleep
while it hides from the cold.
If you're loud,
it'll still wake up.
[SUGIMOTO]
Yep, There's icicles.
And a whole bunch of
half-eaten bamboo.
Is there a bear?
[SUGIMOTO]
Might be.
[ASIRPA]
Wanna catch it?
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
Seriously?
[ASIRPA] We'll put stakes
over the entrance to seal it.
The bear will get nervous
and poke its head out,
then we hit it with
a poison arrow.
My father was braver
than most men.
He would take the poison
arrow with him into the den
and wait for the chance
to kill the bear himself.
[ASIRPA] There's an
Ainu saying about that.
If a human enters the den of a
bear, their life will be spared.
[SUGIMOTO]
Like hell I'm doing that.
I mean, it's not like we're
gonna starve if we don't eat
that bear right now.
So, let's go.
[SUGIMOTO]
Are bears even tasty?
[ASIRPA] Yeah, the brains
are pretty good with salt.
Why'd you stop?
What's wrong?
Over there. What is that?
[ASIRPA]
Something's shining.
It's around the area where
we were this morning.
[SUGIMOTO]
Damn it!
Those are binoculars!
[SUGIMOTO]
How many?
There're three. No, maybe four!
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
Why'd I let my guard down?
[ASIRPA gasps] Quick!
Run through that bamboo grove!
It'll make you harder to track,
which'll slow them down.
[SUGIMOTO]
We're not gonna make it.
Asirpa, I think we
have to split up.
Most likely, they'll only
follow the adult.
Here. It might be best
if you hang on to this.
If they catch you, hand it over
to them without resisting.
Pretend you know nothing.
They're not the kind of
people who'd kill a kid,
so just do what
I'm telling you. Got it?
[ASIRPA]
Sugimoto!
Don't even think about
fighting them. You'll be killed.
C'mon, I'm the
Immortal Sugimoto.
[NOMA]
Found some tracks. Over here.
Looks like they split up.
The kid's that way.
Good, I'll leave her to you.
The rest of you, follow me.
[TANIGAKI] She concealed
her steps. Smart girl.
Too bad for her I'm
from a Matagi family.
I've seen animals pull that
stunt a hundred times.
In order to evade pursuit,
you walk backwards,
carefully stepping into
your own footprints,
then jump in a stand of bamboo.
Come down, kid. I promise
I'm not here to hurt you.
[ASIRPA speaking Ainu]
[TANIGAKI] That's right,
the language barrier.
Look, I'm not going
to eat you. Come on.
Just hand it over to
them without resisting.
Here. I'll catch you.
[TANIGAKI] I'm only
interested in your friend.
[TANIGAKI]
Who was that you were with?
Hm?
[gasps]
[TANIGAKI] Impossible. What is
a child doing with this?
Go ahead and drop the bow, kid.
[ASIRPA gasps]
I knew it... You understand
me perfectly well.
Throw your quiver and
blades to the ground.
[gasps]
[SUGIMOTO pants]
[NOMA]
Stop!
Drop the gun, now.
The bayonet, too.
Why are you running?
[SUGIMOTO]
Why?
I figure you're out here
looking for poachers, right?
And I've been
hunting forbidden game.
That little Ainu
kid was my guide.
[TAMAI]
Hm... Damn waste of my time.
I've seen him before.
It was back in Port Arthur
at the field hospital.
Sugimoto, from the first
division. Immortal Sugimoto.
[BOTH gasp]
[TAMAI] When he woke up, Private
Ogata used all the remaining
strength he had to write
one word: immortal.
You're the one who attacked
Private Ogata that day,
aren't you, Sugimoto?
[OKADA]
Get down on the ground
and put your hands
behind your head!
Get on the ground immediately,
that's an order!
[NOMA]
Do as you're told!
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
Waste of time. I say we should
just shoot out his knees.
[SUGIMOTO gasps, grunts]
[ALL]
Huh?
Ya know what, screw it.
I am... immortal!
He ran into that hole.
Yeah, how pathetic.
Should we smoke him out?
[OKADA] Nah, forget that.
Let's just shoot.
[NOMA] But if he dies, we can't
get any info off of him.
[TAMAI] If he's immortal
he can't die, right?
I vote we shoot
him and find out.
[roaring]
[TAMAI groans]
[chokes]
[NOMA yells grunts]
What's wrong? Are you scared?
Don't think for a second that
you can fight the seventh
division and escape unscathed!
Come and get me!
[TANIGAKI grunts]
What the...?
This is an Ezo wolf!
I thought they were extinct!
Retar!
[yells]
[gasps]
Retar, that's enough! Stop!
You're the last of
the horkewkamuy , my friend.
I won't have you becoming
a Wenkamuy for my sake.
I sure appreciate you
saving my life, though.
Well, looks like she was right
about bears not killing people
who come into
their dens I guess.
So... looks like it's
you and me, pal.
Just be warned:
there's a girl who might
wanna put you in a soup.
[ASIRPA gibbers]
That's right. That's the magic
spot. I know what you like.
[SUGIMOTO]
Asirpa!
Good. You're safe.
Oh, it's that white wolf again.
[bear cub growls]
Quiet in there, okay? Let's keep
you secret for a little bit.
[SUGIMOTO]
Is he dead, then?
[ASIRPA] He can't
follow us now, anyway.
We should just leave him here.
That's right. Let's go.
Sugimoto, what is that?
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
[SUGIMOTO yells] I don't know!
It's, uh, nothing!
[ASIRPA] Sugimoto, would you
like to tell me what you're
doing with that bear?
I'll take such good
care of him!
I'm gonna be his new mommy!
[ASIRPA] How do you imagine
you're going to do that?
Do you have any experience
raising baby bears?
Do you even have the slightest
idea what he should be eating?
Okay. You can go ahead and
eat him if you want to.
I just can't do it.
Huh? No, thank you.
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
[ASIRPA]
I'm not going to eat it.
When we capture baby bears,
we don't eat them.
We raise them in our village!
So, let's go! To my kotan !
[speaking Ainu]
[CHILDREN gasp, giggle]
[SUGIMOTO] They don't
seem scared of me at all.
[ASIRPA]
The Ainu are curious people.
They tend to like new things.
[ASIRPA] Huci. My grandmother
on my mother's side.
It's a pleasure, ma'am.
[HUCI speaks Ainu]
I wonder. Would you be willing
to take this little guy?
I'll be leaving soon.
Can't overstay my welcome.
Huci doesn't understand
your language.
She's inviting you to eat
and to stay the night.
[SUGIMOTO]
Thank you very much, ma'am.
[SUGIMOTO] Won't it
cause problems for you?
My staying here in
the village, I mean.
[speaking Ainu]
No, it's okay.
My grandfather was an
important man in the village.
Nobody will give
Huci any trouble.
Look! You see her tattoo?
The more important
that your husband is,
the bigger your tattoo!
And see, everyone's curious,
just like I said they'd be.
[SUGIMOTO]
Uh...
[TANIGAKI] That was a
truly beautiful wolf.
That shiny, silver pelt.
I want it.
[TANIGAKI]
It's my Tohoku Matagi blood.
I'll follow wherever it leads,
and then, I'll kill it.
[SUGIMOTO] Do any other
families live in this house?
No, just Huci. My uncle and his
wife live in a difference cise .
My grandfather died
six years ago now.
My mother fell ill and died very
soon after she gave birth to me.
I never knew her.
[speaking Ainu]
It's not like it's just me!
There are lots of other girls
who say they don't want
their tattoos, either!
You're behind the times!
[HUCI speaks Ainu]
Asirpa, what is she
saying to me?
She says you shouldn't eat poop.
You're misinformed, ma'am!
I don't eat poop.
It's called miso!
[speaking Ainu]
'Scuse me?
She thinks your ears are weird
because they're not like ours.
You see how mine are shaped?
They're round and thick.
I'm Sugimoto, and you?
What's your name?
My name's Osoma!
[SUGIMOTO]
C'mon, that can't be true.
Doesn't that mean "poop"?
[ASIRPA]
It's true.
We give the children filthy
names in the beginning
to keep the demons
of sickness away.
Sitaktak means
"clump of feces".
Somomap ' s a diaper.
And Tennep actually means
"sticky things".
[OSOMA giggles]
[ASIRPA] Around their sixth
birthday, we give them a
real name based on their
personality and things that
may have happened
in their lives.
What was your name when you
were a little girl, Asirpa?
Ekasiotompuy .
"Grandfather's asshole".
[SUGIMOTO] Yeah, if I
was a demon, I'd run.
[SUGIMOTO] What is that
she's feeding him?
It's a mixture of rice
soup and meat broth.
Ah! Hey, tell me something.
I've noticed you haven't
touched the bear.
Don't you like him?
[ASIRPA] It's not that.
It's just you shouldn't be
affectionate with him or
you'll get too attached.
They're released back into
these mountains, right?
They're not. We send
them back to the gods.
It's a traditional ceremony.
Oh, so, in other words...
I had a baby bear.
I took care of him like
I would a little brother.
A year later, just before
the ceremony,
I tried to send him
back to the mountains
and everyone got really mad.
I was so upset, I couldn't
go to his ceremony,
even though I'd never
missed one before.
So you'll kill him after all.
We don't think of it as killing.
We believe we're returning
them to the gods.
The Ainu call everything
in our world that helps us,
or that is beyond
our control, " Kamuy ".
Or Gods. We honor these Kamuy
with ceremonies of thanks,
showing them respect
and devotion.
This maintains a good
relationship with them.
My people are hunters, so animal
kamuy are important to us.
In the land of the gods,
animals have human forms.
We believe they come
to play in our world.
Providing us meat and pelts.
The most important of all is
the Kimun Kamuy . The bear.
To raise a cub is a great honor.
We lovingly care for
them for a year or two.
When we send the bear back,
the whole village comes together
for a huge ceremony.
This is called " iomante ".
We ask them to tell the other
gods that our world is a fun,
joyful place. It is
said that if we do this,
the kamuy will keep
returning to us.
Okay, but do you really
believe all of this?
[ASIRPA]
You have to understand,
our beliefs make up
our way of life.
For example, I believe that
we raise these bear cubs,
because when they're grown,
they in turn provide us with
much needed pelts and meat.
My people have lived this
way for many generations,
so, yes, I believe that
it's true and right.
There's no way to prevent
the sorrow of parting,
I've learned to keep my distance
so I won't get too attached.
That's a very pragmatic
way of thinking.
You know what I bet, Asirpa?
I bet you're not like most
of the other Ainu are you?
My father gifted me
with the name, "Asirpa".
Its literal meaning
is "a new year".
But it can also mean
"the future".
I believe that I am an
Ainu girl for a new era!
[SOLDIER A] Lieutenant Tsurumi,
it's going to be difficult
to do any more
tracking in this snow.
None of those men are
here in these mountains
for the very first time.
After all, we know
Tanigaki is a Matagi.
It's hard to imagine
that he could be lost.
[WADA]
Tsurumi! Bastard!
What are you doing taking my
men out on a day like this?
[TSURUMI] Captain Wada!
What a surprise to see you.
[WADA] One man in critical
condition! Four missing!
On top of that, I heard you
brought a giant arsenal
of weapons in from Asahikawa!
You're going to pay
for this, Tsurumi!
Oh, please forgive me.
A shell fragment blew
off the front of my skull
in the Battle of Mukden,
and sometimes things leak out
at the most
inappropriate moments.
Do you actually think you can
continue to be a lieutenant?
There's no place in
the army for you now!
Get the hell out of my face!
[WADA screams]
Tsurumi! Have you gone mad?
[WADA groans]
[TSURUMI] I lost a bit of
my frontal lobe, you see.
I'm afraid that it's done
horrible things to my temper.
Beyond that, I'm the
picture of good health.
Wounds to the body,
are like a medal.
I feel a nice injury
improves one's looks, see?
You've gone
completely insane. Fire!
Sir!
[TSURUMI] Strip him of his
uniform and bury him.
Our comrades still lie just
beneath the Manchurian wastes.
Our war is not over yet.
Not by a long shot.
[USHIYAMA, WOMAN B groan]
Your ridiculous libido has
gotten the better of you,
Ushiyama the Undefeated.
How did you find me?
You sold me out, didn't you?
You're hurting me!
Stop, you're gonna break it!
Old man Hikikata.
Did you think you could
shatter my hard head?
Of course.
Look at this, Ushiyama.
You put oiled paper
against their body
and copy the tattoos
when they show through.
That gives you a
fairly accurate copy.
Then there's no
need to kill them.
Help me out.
What we need is a relationship
of mutual interest.
Start by telling me what
you're gathering people for.
[HIJIKATA]
At some point,
we're going to have to face
the Seventh Division.
We'll have to steal
the tattooed skins
that they've already taken.
You're planning on
facing the Imperial Army,
and you're gonna do it with an
obsolete weapon like a katana?
Have you lost your mind?
[HIJIKATA] No matter how
old he might happen to be,
a boy always loves the chance
to swing a katana, right?
♪
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "Grim Reaper".