[ASIRPA]
Look, Sugimoto.
These are all pine cones
that have been eaten.
There are lots of them.
[ASIRPA] The Ezo Pines are
feeding grounds for squirrels.
If we lay a stick
up against the trunk,
the squirrels will get lazy and
use it to climb up the tree.
Never fails.
Then we put kukuri traps made
out of wire on the stick.
When the squirrels put
their heads through,
it strangles them.
[SUGIMOTO chuckles]
You eat squirrels, huh?
I'm afraid I like 'em too much.
I like them, too.
They only eat nuts, you see,
so the meat's great.
And you can sell their
pelts for a fair sum.
I hope we catch a lot.
[SUGIMOTO]
Yeah...
[ASIRPA]
Let's set some more traps.
[SUGIMOTO] If the escaped
prisoners are out looking
for the gold, my bet is
they'll stay in Hokkaido.
I'll find them, no question.
[ASIRPA]
Hokkaido is a big place.
[SUGIMOTO] Yeah, the prisoners
aren't wild animals, though.
They won't be able to survive
hidden in the mountains
for long. In a small village,
an outsider will stand out.
An escaped prisoner is likely
to hide in a large town
where he can blend in easier.
So, what are the most
populated cities in Hokkaido?
Sapporo, Hakodate, Asahikawa.
And this place.
[SUGIMOTO]
Otaru.
♪
[NARRATOR] The last days
of the Meiji era,
Otaru had grown into
a financial center so
powerful that it was called
"The Wall Street of the North".
The largest commercial
city in Hokkaido,
its bustle a contrast to the
neighboring Ainu villages.
[SUGIMOTO]
Hey, do you come here often?
You seen any customers around
the place with weird tattoos?
[MAN A]
Hm. What kind?
[SUGIMOTO] Pretty different
from the ones the yakuza's have.
They're kind of an interesting
mix of lots of curves
and straight lines.
Huh... Nah, doesn't
sound familiar.
You looking for
somebody specific?
No. Forget about it.
Huh. Well, damn, I guess
you're a soldier.
I've never seen anybody with
those tattoos, but I've sure as
hell never seen a guy with scars
like the ones you've got.
We never would've gotten
Karafuto back if it weren't
for you men and
your sacrifices.
Thank you. We owe
you a great deal.
Any customers with
tattoos like this?
[WOMAN A] Hm. No. I'd remember
a design like that.
It's not the kind of
thing you forget.
[MAN B]
Hey!
What business does a
mangy Ainu brat have
hanging around in
front of my shop?
Just leave her alone,
the poor thing.
Look at that, you don't
have your tattoo yet.
I'm told Ainu women tattoo
the skin around their mouth
when they're old
enough to get married.
But I guess that would
scare off the customers,
so maybe I'll
sell you, instead!
[MAN B groans]
My eye!
You stupid brat!
[SUGIMOTO]
Hey.
[MAN B]
Huh?
Turn around and
look at my thumb.
Huh? Just who the hell are you?
[groans]
You ever see a tattoo like this?
[MAN B grunts]
[SUGIMOTO] Hmph. Makes sense
to avoid a bathhouse.
They'd have to show their skin.
Hold on. There was another man.
He asked... He asked
me the same question!
Heh. Sounds like we
had the same idea.
[MAN C] A tattoo?
Sorry, but I can't help you.
[SUGIMOTO] It's alright.
Thanks anyway.
[SUGIMOTO]
How many are there?
I only see one.
[MAN D] I was gonna wait
till they made camp,
but it doesn't look like they're
stopping anytime soon.
We should just get it over with.
[MAN D groans]
[SUGIMOTO] Got him.
There's our first one!
--[grunts]
--[clicking]
Where are all the
other prisoners?
[MAN D]
Heh.
The way I understand it,
you need all the tattoos
to decrypt the code.
So, you'd have to
stick together.
Yeah, well, I thought the
same thing in the beginning.
Why did you leave, then?
[MAN D]
We turned on each other.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
Don't know why.
Without any kinda warning,
everyone started
killing each other.
I didn't know what
was happening, so I ran.
Hid out up here on my own.
Knew I couldn't trust anyone.
I see.
Sounds like one of the prisoners
figured out the ugly truth.
[MAN D]
Huh?
[SUGIMOTO]
What, you really don't know?
Hate to tell you this, but those
tattoos are only usable if you
kill the owner and skin them.
[MAN D chuckles]
That brutal bastard.
So, what? You and your friend
planning to hunt us down
one by one, then?
You'd be a helluva lot better
off hunting rabbits, mister!
You satisfied with
those last words?
[gasps]
Don't worry.
Once you're dead,
it won't hurt a bit when I
slowly rip off your skin.
[grunts]
[ASIRPA] Sugimoto. You promised
me you wouldn't kill him.
If you do this,
I won't help you.
[SUGIMOTO]
Aw, come on.
Would it have been that
difficult to play along?
I'd say two to three minutes and
he would've started talking.
[gasps]
[SUGIMOTO] You've really
got a talent for this.
That's great work.
This tool is what's great.
You said "pencil", right?
Genius.
[ASIRPA gasps]
[ASIRPA] My father was good
with his hands, too.
So the women loved him.
The Ainu men, they give
makiri they make themselves
to the women they love.
The women look at
how well-made it is
to determine if the man
can support them.
My father made me this.
My menoko makiri .
[ASIRPA] What kind of
man carved that tattoo?
Nopperabo.
[BOTH gasp]
What does that mean?
He had no face.
[gunshot echos]
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
No.
Who's out there?
Someone was with him.
[gasps] Hey, what're you doing?
He'll shoot you!
[ASIRPA]
Making a smoke screen.
I'll cover you, but hurry up!
[OGATA]
A type 26 revolver.
No way the bullets can
reach me at 300 meters.
[OGATA]
Huh?
She's burning green wood.
[OGATA gasps]
[grunts]
[OGATA]
What?
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[grunting]
[SUGIMOTO] I planned to
take him alive, but...
[SUGIMOTO] I can't beat
him if I hold back!
[SUGIMOTO]
Move and I'll shoot!
[OGATA chuckels]
[gasps]
[SUGIMOTO]
A soldier. I knew it.
And the Regiment Number
on his epaulet.
The Hokkaido Seventh Division,
the strongest in the army!
[NARRATOR] The Imperial Japanese
Army's Seventh Division.
During the Russo-Japanese War,
they were sent to the
deadliest battlefields.
Suffering heavy losses,
they contributed to
numerous victories.
They are the army's
strongest division.
The people of
Hokkaido call them
the Guardians of the North,
with both fear and respect.
[SUGIMOTO]
These prisoners are dangerous,
but we don't need these
guys as enemies, either.
So then. What unit
were you with?
I used to be with the first.
But my term was up, so I left.
I see.
Then there's a good possibility
you and I met at 2-0-3 hill.
You're taking a mighty
big gamble here,
and I don't think you
understand how dangerous it is.
You really that greedy?
[SUGIMOTO] Nope... I'm doing
it for the girl I love.
[grunting]
Sugimoto!
[OGATA]
Sugimoto of the First Division?
The Immortal Sugimoto?
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[OGATA grunts]
He'll fall!
[SUGIMOTO]
If he'd managed to escape,
his friends would've
come after us.
This was prob'ly for the best.
"Immortal Sugimoto".
What does that mean?
In all my time at the front,
I only learned one
way not to die.
Don't let them kill you.
Asirpa, I'm not a murderer.
But if someone wants me dead,
I'm gonna kill them first.
"The weak will be eaten."
That's the same everywhere,
a universal truth.
[stomach growls]
[SUGIMOTO] How are you
hungry at a time like this?
[ASIRPA] I'm alive.
Of course I'm hungry.
We can make dinner
at my hunting tent.
We'll eat the squirrels
we trapped. Some chitatap .
Chitatap ?
Yes. It's an Ainu dish.
Freshly ground meat.
Here, watch this.
First, you skin them.
Once you score the pelt, you can
peel it off like clothing.
Squeeze out the contents of
the organs and wash them clean.
The gall bladder's bitter,
so we remove it.
Usually, you toss the
brain into the chitatap ,
but it's delicious alone.
Sugimoto, you should
have the brain.
Uh! You mean you
want me to eat it
before it's been cooked?
What are you saying?
Do you have a problem
with the way the Ainu eat?
Uh... Well, no.
It's just a little different
than what I'm used to.
[ASIRPA]
Good. Then eat the brain.
How is it?
[ASIRPA]
Squirrels are small,
so we chop the meat
with a tashiro .
A chitatap is chopped
up very finely,
so you can eat
the entire animal,
none of it goes to waste.
You're so knowledgeable
about this stuff.
Who taught you how to hunt?
Father.
I don't have brothers, so he
took me with him to hunt.
I like the mountains
better than weaving.
Staying home never suited me.
So, it worked well.
It's your turn now.
Chitatap means
"something we carve together".
The "we" is because
we take turns chopping.
Say " chitatap " as you do it.
Chitatap , chitatap ,
chitatap, chitatap ...
[ASIRPA] Chitatap is only
made from fresh kills.
You eat it raw, after all.
But since you're a rich
and refined Sisam
and not used to that,
I'm adding it to an ohau .
Fish ball soup, but with meat.
That sounds great.
[ASIRPA] The blood and bones
went into the chitatap , too.
But they'll soak up the
flavor of the salty broth.
Looks good, thank you.
Wow! It's amazing!
[SUGIMOTO] This meat is
delicious. It's almost sweet!
And the tiny chopped bones
actually give it a nice,
crunchy texture!
Hinna , hinna .
Hey, what's " hinna " mean?
For my people, it's a
word of thanks.
Something we say to the food.
Hinna .
Hinna , hinna .
[SUGIMOTO]
[SOLDIER A]
We found him on the riverbank
shortly after nightfall.
Any later and he most likely
would've died of hypothermia.
[CAPTAIN WADA] Somebody attacked
him in the mountains, then?
Would anyone care to
explain why Private Ogata
was out there by himself?
[SHIRAISHI groans]
That's two.
[groaning continues]
So did you run from the
other prisoners when they
turned on each other, too?
Tell me, how many men are there?
Where were you prisoners
supposed to be meeting
Nopperabo's friends?
Did the trap crush
his vocal chords?
I'll tell you if you let
me borrow your pet Ainu.
How 'bout if I break
your jaw instead,
so you'll never be
able to talk again?
[ASIRPA] Let it go.
I don't care what he says.
I'm used to it.
[SHIRAISHI grunts]
You should never have
had to get used to it.
Sugimoto!
[SUGIMOTO]
Hm?
Look! See that rabbit?
A rabbit? Where is it?
[ASIRPA] The ears are right
there. They have black tips.
[SUGIMOTO]
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Damn, I can't hit it now.
I don't want to just wound it.
[ASIRPA] When a rabbit's running
around during the day,
that means bad weather's coming
and it's looking to hide.
I say we catch him and hole up
in the tent for the day.
[grunts]
[NARRATOR]
Yoshitake Shiraishi.
A master escape artist who was
more commonly known as...
..."The Escape King".
[ASIRPA]
You're mine!
There, I told you! I got it!
Behind you!
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh? What? How the--?
[ASIRPA] Be careful!
Don't forget! The weather!
Go on ahead to
the tent, Asirpa!
Don't worry, I'm gonna
catch this guy!
But I wanted to eat
the rabbit right now.
[SHIRAISHI grunts]
What a bastard. Get up
here or I'll shoot!
Go right ahead! Do you really
think I give a rat's ass
whether I get shot now or later?
[crackling]
Gunshots?
Nipusfum .
[NARRATOR]
In the language of the Ainu,
Nipusfum means "The Sound
of the Splitting Trees."
A cold wave of
negative 30 degrees
Celsius brings a rapid
drop in temperature,
freezing the water
contained within the trees,
causing their trunks to shatter.
[SUGIMOTO]
Wait, damn it!
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[SHIRAISHI]
Huh?
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
[BOTH yell]
[gasps] This is very bad!
Oh, god, I'm freezing!
[SHIRAISHI gasps]
It's too cold! It's too cold!
My head feels like
it's splitting!
[SUGIMOTO] Fire! We need to
start a fire or we're gonna die!
Now!
[SUGIMOTO groans]
No use!
[NARRATOR]
Soaked and freezing,
they had only 10 minutes before
death would claim them.
Let's rub wood together
and start a fire.
[NARRATOR]
Hypothermia causes confusion.
[SUGIMOTO] That isn't
going to work, you idiot!
[NARRATOR] It also produces
an unconcerned expression.
Oh, right! My gun, damn!
Where the hell did my gun go?
No, is that it?
My bullets! I musta
dropped 'em! Damn it!
What do I do? I will
not give up! I refuse!
I won't die here, not me!
Because I'm the
Immortal Sugimoto!
[SUGIMOTO groans]
Wait! What are you doing?
[SUGIMOTO gasps] Hey, you!
If you don't wanna die,
find the bullets that
fell into the river!
We should be able to use the
gunpowder that's inside.
Okay. We'll make a deal.
I'll help you now, but only
if you let me live later!
You can shove that
deal right up your ass!
Now help me, or we're
both going to die.
Are you gonna take the deal
or not? It's up to you!
Fine! Just get in the
river and start looking
for those damn bullets, already!
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
Haha, here we go.
I've got this in case I ever
need to shoot the lock
off of a jail cell.
It's so cold, I forgot I had it.
[SUGIMOTO pants]
Okay. I think we're ready.
[BOTH laugh victoriously]
[SHIRAISHI] There are 24
tattooed prisoners, all in all.
How many are actually still
alive is anyone's guess.
As for Nopperabo's friends,
I really have no idea.
The only one who could even
possibly know at this point is
the leader of the prisoners,
who led the escape.
This leader,
tell me about him.
At first, I thought he was
just an old political prisoner.
A quiet, model captive.
But it turns out, he had us all
fooled from the beginning.
I watched him steal a sword
off one of the soldiers
right in front of me.
In less than a second,
three men were dead.
It was later, that I found out
that he was a survivor of the
Hakodate War, 30 years ago.
A samurai from
the old shogunate.
But the interesting thing about
that is, I was told that
according to the records, he
actually died during that war.
The Demon Vice Commander
of the Shinsengumi,
Toshizou Hijikata.
[SHIRAISHI] There isn't
much else I can tell you.
Except for this.
The instruction that
Nopperabo gave everyone:
"Get yourself to Otaru."
[SUGIMOTO] Shiraishi.
That's your name, isn't it?
Give up on the Ainu gold
and get out of Hokkaido.
It's not just the
other prisoners and
Nopperabo's friends who are
after the tattoos, you know.
The Seventh Division
is back from the war,
and they've got
plans of their own.
Yeah, but I'm the
Escape King.
No matter who catches me, I'll
disappear like smoke in the air.
See you around,
Immortal Sugimoto!
[knocking]
[MAN E] Lieutenant Tsurumi!
Ogata has woken up, sir!
[TSURUMI] Very good.
Then I'll pay him a visit.
♪
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "Kamuy Mosir."