[TETSUZOU]
See that?
That's the face of a bear
that would kill a man.
[TANIGAKI]
How can you tell?
[TETSUZOU]
Easy.
A six-year-old female who's
obviously never given birth.
Beasts like this only get
more violent over time.
When it comes to brown bears,
females are always
more foul-tempered.
They're kinda like
humans that way
[laughs]
[TETSUZOU] As a Matagi,
you probably know this,
but no two bears
are exactly alike.
Some get scared and run.
Others come after you no matter
how many times you shoot 'em.
I must've killed over
200 of 'em, myself,
but the hunt has never
been the same twice.
[TANIGAKI]
He's killed 200 Himself?
Although, they tend to
have similar habits.
If you know those habits inside
and out, that can go a long way
towards getting you
out of a bind.
So, Matagi soldier,
you've never hunted wolf before,
isn't that right?
No, what about you?
Nah... I know nothing.
That's why I want to hunt one.
[wolf howls]
[TETSUZOU]
Over time,
human traps have driven
the wolves to extinction.
But one last wolf fought
that battle of wits
and came out alive.
The lone survivor.
The thought of going head to
head with him is irresistible.
It gets my hunter's soul erect.
♪
See the footprints towards
that Sakhalin fir?
The deer you shot must be
taking refuge down there.
I'll drive it out. Then, you can
go around and ambush it.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
Right.
[SUGIMOTO] This time, I gotta
put it out of its misery.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
Whoa!
[ASIRPA]
It's on the move!
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
Where is it?
Where the hell
did that thing go?
It climbed up that way.
I'm amazed it still has
that much stamina.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
It'll be dark soon. I think
we should wait 'til morning.
We'll be able to track
it more easily, then.
[ASIRPA] Don't beat
yourself up so much.
It won't be a total waste.
Deer meat isn't
good if it suffers,
but the brain and eyeballs
will still be delicious.
[SUGIMOTO] Yeah, that's not
exactly the point.
[TETSUZOU] Tonight, you'll dine
on freshly killed bear,
prepared by none other
than Tetsuzou Nihei.
Behold: Nihei's cuisine!
You ready? Have some heart!
Good, right? The more you chew,
the bloodier it tastes.
Fresh heart is a treat
only hunters get to enjoy,
huh, Tanigaki?
I've heard the Matagi
drink bear blood, right?
Then you oughta appreciate this.
Nihei's cuisine!
Tasty blood sausage!
[TETSUZOU]
Mm. Nice and bloody.
Be careful, it boosts
the libido.
Don't you go blowing a
huge hole through my roof.
With your hard-on!
[laughs]
[TANIGAKI groans]
[TETSUZOU]
You're a quiet one.
The Matagi ways have
seeped into your bones.
Tell me, why's a fellow like
you still wearing that cap?
Doesn't suit you at all.
Why don't you go
back home, Tanigaki?
[TANIGAKI] I stayed in the
military for a reason.
I had no desire to
go home to Akita.
But then, when I was
in the mountains,
there was a heaviness. It felt
like my body was full of poison.
"May you be born again, and may
you awaken to pleasant sounds."
That's what we Matagi
say to the bears
as we send them
to the next life.
I never said that to
any man I killed,
and something about
that seems wrong.
[TETSUZOU]
Now I understand.
The wolf hunt is just
an excuse for you.
You can't go back
to the military,
and you can't go back home.
Your hunter's soul wanders
the forests of Hokkaido.
[TETSUZOU] Tanigaki,
when we kill that wolf,
you take its pelt and head home.
[TETSUZOU]
Hm.
[TANIGAKI chuckels]
[laughs]
[TETSUZOU]
Hard-on!
[SOLDIER A]
Stand up, Sugimoto!
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[SOLDIERS shouting, yelling]
[SUGIMOTO] Run, run!
You stop, you're dead!
I refuse to die! I will live!
[gasps]
This is where the deer dug up
the snow and went to sleep.
We were a little too late.
This is frozen deer osoma .
Here, take a look.
And don't eat it.
It's not the kind
you're supposed to eat.
I told you it's not poop!
[ASIRPA] Deer drop osoma
at regular intervals,
so that makes it easy to tell
how far away you are.
This spacing is close.
We'll catch it for sure.
[TANIGAKI] How do you
plan to hunt the wolf?
[TETSUZOU] First, we need
some bait to lure it out.
We'll shoot a deer.
[TANIGAKI] Why? We have
plenty of bear meat.
[TETSUZOU] If you were
walking down the road
and you saw a peeled
persimmon lying on the ground,
would you pick it up and eat it?
When you're hunting,
you need to put yourself
in the place of the prey.
Did you lose your touch in
the war, Mister Matagi-man?
[ASIRPA]
Its tracks are unsteady.
It's finally running
out of strength.
[ASIRPA] See that tree?
That must be where it's hiding.
I'll chase it out.
You go downwind, circle around
a good long ways,
then lay in ambush.
Stay low and go quiet.
[SUGIMOTO] I'll do it
in one shot this time.
I refuse to make it
suffer any more.
Ryuu's pretty young,
but he's a good hunting dog.
His nose is powerful.
It can pick up the newest,
strongest scent among
the deer tracks, easy.
What is it, Ryuu?
[RYUU whimpers]
[TETSUZOU]
I see.
This is a dog that doesn't fear
bears, and look at him, now.
[TANIGAKI gasps]
Do you mean?
[TETSUZOU chuckles]
[TETSUZOU]
We've entered wolf territory!
[ASIRPA]
Here we go, Sugimoto. Be sharp.
[coughs]
[gasps]
Take the shot!
[ASIRPA]
What is he doing?
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
Retar?
[ASIRPA]
Hold it down Retar!
Why didn't you shoot?
You swore you'd finish it!
The blood from its wound,
it had become an icicle.
It didn't even have enough
body heat left to melt it,
but it was still
determined to live.
When it looked at me,
I couldn't move.
This deer is me.
[deer bellows]
If you can't
take responsibility,
don't shoot at all.
[TANIGAKI] That gunshot. It was
a Type 30, just like mine.
[ASIRPA] Come here.
Put your hands inside.
[gasps]
[ASIRPA]
Well?
It's so warm.
My hands are warm again.
[ASIRPA]
That's right.
This deer died and
now it's warming you.
Its body heat is becoming
yours and keeping you alive.
We and the other animals
will eat the meat.
The rest will feed the trees,
and the grass, and the earth.
The value of the deer's
life still goes on.
[SUGIMOTO]
Should we eat it?
[ASIRPA gasps]
Yes! Let's!
[SUGIMOTO]
Hm? Retar's acting strange.
[ASIRPA]
Hm?
He's warning us.
Someone's coming.
It must be that soldier.
Why is he still looking for me?
Go ahead. Go.
[ASIRPA] Let's grab what we
can and get out of here.
Retar will come back later
and finish off the rest.
You don't mean this, right?
[ASIRPA] We're eating
the brains. Bring it.
[TETSUZOU] Look. Wolf tracks.
And big ones, at that.
Hmm. There's no
sign of it feeding.
Did it make the kill and then
some hunters took the meat?
Piss poor job cleaning up.
[TANIGAKI]
A Type 30 rifle and boots,
and a child wearing
deerskin shoes.
Those two from before.
Must be them.
Are you talking
about the Ainu girl?
I don't really know why,
but that wolf doesn't
seem to fear the girl.
However, it sensed us and ran.
Sounds to me like they left
the meat behind for the wolf.
Maybe it'll head back
here to eat it, then.
Tanigaki. I think it's
time for a bath.
[TANIGAKI]
Huh?
Matagi always bathe in
cold water before hunting,
don't they?
We're up against a wolf
with a sharp sense of smell.
We need to do everything
we can to prepare.
[SUGIMOTO]
It's too far away to see much,
but one is carrying
soldier's gear.
At least they don't seem to
be following us. Let's go.
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[SUGIMOTO]
Someone's here.
It's about time.
[SUGIMOTO]
Oh. It's you.
[SHIRAISHI]
What kinda greeting is that?
Oh, you got a fresh kill?
Talk about perfect timing!
I brought some saké to
warm us all up tonight!
[ASIRPA]
Deer lung. You eat this raw.
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
[SHIRAISHI] Why do I have
to chop this, again?
[ASIRPA]
It's chitatap !
[ALL laughing]
Hey, Sugimoto, there's still
some chitatap . Finish it off.
Can't fit another
bite in my belly.
What?
[SHIRAISHI groans]
We will honor the
deer who died today!
The heat of its organs
and taste of its meat!
It's all proof that
the deer lived!
Eat it and remember it all!
That is how we take
responsibility for our prey!
If I were to die,
would you forget me?
Or would you be
the one who didn't?
[ASIRPA]
Huh? Why would you say that?
Don't die, Sugimoto!
I am immortal!
[ASIRPA sobs]
See? He won't die.
Now, open wide.
Chitatap makes
everything better.
Chitatap ' s the best!
[SHIRAISHI]
Oh, right, I almost forgot.
I'm here for a reason.
I wanted to tell you
something I heard in town.
[SUGIMOTO]
Hm?
Information about one of
those tattooed prisoners
you two've been looking for.
I heard it from
a pelt trader.
A man who'd been arrested for
three murders several years ago
apparently showed
back up in Otaru.
He was a famously
talented hunter,
feared and respected enough
by the pelt traders that they
gave him a second name.
"The Hunter Who Gives
Hibernating Bears Bad Dreams".
Otherwise known
as Tetsuzou Nihei.
One of those tattoos.
[TETSUZOU] Hey, don't you
look at me like that.
So much judgement. It's only
small because of the cold.
Trust me, it's usually
a monster.
How do you dare joke with me,
after you murdered
those soldiers.
You gonna shoot and
skin me right here?
Then run on back
to the military?
Matagi, or soldier? Which one
are you right now, boy?
That's what you've got
to decide for yourself.
Tetsuzou Nihei. I know where
I've heard that name before.
[SHIRAISHI, SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
[ASIRPA] There used to be this
group of men who'd kill hunters
and steal their prey.
But then, one time it was pretty
clear they picked the wrong
guy to go after.
I'd tracked and slain
a bear that left its den
and was field dressing it.
That's when it happened.
[TETSUZOU]
Can you hear me, thieves?
When I hunt a bear, I'm willing
to risk my life doing it,
you damn cowards!
If you wanna try and hunt me,
you'd better be prepared to
end up a piece of animal shit!
[TETSUZOU]
You're lower than animals.
I won't waste a bullet.
[gasps]
[TETSUZOU] I spent three days
tracking them, one by one.
and beating them to death.
But the last one, the police
that were searching the mountain
got to him first.
Oh, you finally made it, Nihei!
Looks like you're too late.
[OFFICER A]
Hey, put the club down!
Halt! Stop where you are!
Please, you need to
leave him to us, now.
[MAN C laughs]
[TETSUZOU] I'm more obsessed
with tracking my prey
than any bear. Although,
unfortunately, I'm not a bear.
I'm human. And human beings have
their own laws, don't they?
My penalty for following
the law of the mountains
was to be sent to
Abashiri Prison.
I escaped because I wanted
to die in the mountains.
At the end of my journey,
the beasts of the wild will
eat me and shit me out, and I'll
become part of the land.
That's my ideal end.
You can understand that, right?
Tanigaki Matagi?
So, he's an older man
and he has an Ainu dog.
The guy from earlier.
Oh, also, there was
one more thing.
He asked the pelt trader
something interesting.
He said, "If I had
a white wolf pelt,
what would you pay for it?"
[ASIRPA] Why didn't you
tell us that first?!
[ASIRPA] It wasn't me, after
all. They were after Retar.
Asirpa, we'll go tomorrow.
We have to get some sleep.
[ASIRPA breathes unevenly]
[SUGIMOTO] This is it. A clue
to the gold's location.
At this point,
he won't be much use,
except to keep you warm.
You'll tell me if the
wolf comes, won't you?
[RYUU growls]
Wolf droppings. He got us.
When could he have?
[TETSUZOU]
If he's smart,
he did it when we were bathing.
[TANIGAKI]
A "watching wolf."
[TETSUZOU]
Hm?
[TANIGAKI] I've heard stories
about wolves that track humans
and study them.
And we were watched from the
first moment we came here,
weren't we?
I'm getting hard again.
When a watching wolf
comes after you,
you're supposed to
take off your clothes,
and the wolf stays focused
on those rather than you.
If I had to bet, I'd say
he's watching us, now.
[gasps, grunts]
What the hell is that stink?
[TETSUZOU]
The droppings he kindly left.
I'm gonna convince
him we're intruders
and hopefully drive him
to obsess over us.
Take it in. This is the last
fire made with wolf droppings
that there'll ever be in Japan!
[ASIRPA] That's where we
hunted the deer yesterday.
[TETSUZOU] Both you and I have a
pretty murderous air about us.
That's probably why
the wolf found us.
[TANIGAKI] There's a
Matagi word: " kibake ,"
which means to become a tree.
When you wait for your prey,
you become one with the
trees to stay hidden.
" Kibake ", huh?
[SUGIMOTO]
It's them.
[SHIRAISHI] How'm I supposed
to see their faces
if they won't look this way?
Asirpa, have your bow
ready for backup.
[SHIRAISHI grunts]
[ASIRPA] He's focused.
He's found his target.
What is he aiming at?
[ASIRPA]
Retar! Stay back!
[TETSUZOU] There he is.
Why won't he move?
He's sensed the
danger in me.
Gotta control my emotions.
Kibake ! Kibake !
[TETSUZOU]
There you are.
What the hell happened?
[SUGIMOTO]
Throw that gun over here.
[TETSUZOU] Guess my kibake ' s
pretty lousy considering you
obviously found me so easy.
[SUGIMOTO]
This is him, right?
Yeah, no doubt.
This is Tetsuzou Nihei.
Shiraishi, huh?
I'm gonna take a wild guess
and say you're after my tattoo.
[SUGIMOTO] So you gonna keep
your hand on that rifle?
Because I guarantee you, in the
time it takes to get a bullet
out of your pouch, pull back
the bolt, and load it,
I'll easily have five
rounds inside you.
Why not go ahead and try it.
Let's just see which one
of us survives out here.
Well, the thing is,
I'm immortal.
[RYUU barks]
[TETSUZOU]
Good job, boy!
[grunting]
I hope you're ready for your
new existence as animal shit,
poor bastard!
♪
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "Complication".