♪
[birds chirping]
[MANA] That's Collette,
the Maiden of Aquarius.
She's respected and well-loved
by everyone in town.
These days, she runs the bakery
for her grandfather,
who's fallen ill.
Innocent and honorable
to her core,
she knows nothing of
the corruption in the world.
I mean, she's the kind
of girl
who thinks babies are delivered
to cabbage fields by storks!
She's like everyone's
favorite little sister!
You know the type.
Wow.
You'll be responsible for
corrupting a young girl's mind!
Maybe even inspiring her
first impure thoughts!
It'll be like stepping
on undisturbed snow, you know?
Beautiful!
All that fresh, new energy.
Urges going haywire,
full of desire,
crotches on fire!
Pretty great!
Don't you think?
[ITSUKI]
I don't.
I know it's all in order
to cleanse
the Impurities from this world.
But this sweet girl,
so full of wonder.
Is she ready?
I wouldn't want to
push anything, you know?
I can't see Collette
that way. She's pure.
Are you implying that the rest
of the maidens are impure?
You might want to check yourself
and remember,
the Love Ritual is sacred!
[ITSUKI grunts]
[ITSUKI] I don't know
what I should do!
[MANA] I'll tell you
what you should do!
Your duty! Now, focus!
-Get your ass over there!
-[ITSUKI grunts]
[COLLETTE] Makin' the bread.
Rollin' the dough.
Oh.
[ITSUKI]
Collette.
Is it okay if I leave
the flour here?
Yeah. That's fine.
[ITSUKI] What would you like me
to do next?
Well, um, are you sure you want
to stick around?
You really don't have to
help out here, you know.
You must be busy
with your duties as Visitor.
Please don't worry about it.
I'm helping out
because I want to.
But...
It's just...
The only reason you're spending
time with me at all,
is because you want me to make
a Star Child with you, isn't it?
[shouts]
Knowing that's why you're here
makes me kinda nervous.
It's just hard to work.
Things are slow, I know.
But I still have to run
the whole bakery.
[ITSUKI] It's not like that!
I really want... yeah!
I do, I want to help you,
Collette!
Why, though?
I don't get it.
You started work before dawn,
but you've been smiling all day.
People come in here
to buy your bread,
and they leave
with that smile.
I think that's really amazing.
That's why I want to stay
and help.
That's so nice.
But, still, you are planning
to make a Star Child with me.
Oh, no!
I don't have any intention of...
Well, no, I do, but...
That's in the distant future,
once we've gotten to know
each other,
and we're feeling
more comfortable.
Oh, okay.
Well, you do seem
like an honest kind of person.
I admit, that's a relief.
I'm looking forward to helping
however I can!
I'm looking forward
to it, as well.
[ITSUKI] Baking's actually
a lot of physical work, huh?
It must be tough doing it
on your own.
No way. I adore it.
You see, it's always been
my dream to bake bread!
-Your dream?
-Oh, yes!
I've always loved the idea
of people having a better day
because of something yummy
I could make for them.
It's the same dream I've had
ever since childhood, so...
[MANA] When I see Collette's
bright, hopeful smile,
I wonder briefly
what it would feel like
to be inside that feeling.
I'm filled with a sudden desire
to have her in my hands,
to knead her body like dough.
[ITSUKI] Don't voice me
without my permission!
[Mana yelling, giggling]
Well, that was weird.
[YUZUHA]
All right, and just hold it.
[COLLETTE]
They've turned out perfectly!
I'll say.
They look great!
Would you like to
try some? Here!
Aah!
Come on, open up!
[ITSUKI]
Uh, sorry.
Hurry up and take
a bite, would ya?
I'm getting a little
self-conscious, here.
Oh. Well...
Okay.
[BOTH]
Aah!
Please be honest.
Does it taste good?
Yeah. It's great.
So glad you like!
[MANA] But unfortunately, bread
will never satisfy me again.
You're the one I want
to feast on now, Collette.
[ITSUKI] Stop it!
I told you not to do that!
[MANA]
No, no, no, no, no!
[giggling]
Can't let my guard
down for a second.
Hey, Collette,
should we go ahead
and set the fresh
baked goods out?
Your customers are waiting.
[COLLETTE]
Sure.
[COLLETTE whimpers]
[ITSUKI]
So, not many customers today.
Maybe there's a big sale on
bread going on somewhere else.
[chuckles]
No. It's been like this
ever since my grandpa got sick.
-Your Grandpa?
-Yes.
[COLLETTE]
He was a brilliant baker,
and there were always
long lines at the bakery.
But, not since I took over.
Maybe I don't have
what it takes to succeed.
That's not true.
[MANA] Her smile had been as
bright as an angel
just a moment ago, but now
she was sad and shivering
like a poor,
pathetic little puppy
getting soaked
out in the rain!
I can definitely think
of a few different ways
to put that smile back
where it belongs!
[ITSUKI] Mana, seriously,
you have to stop!
[MANA]
I'll be back.
If you want me to do the job,
get out of my way.
You okay?
[door bell jingles]
-How's it going?
-We came to see you.
Hey, Mahiru. Arie.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
We're just visiting the bakery.
We heard that you and Collette
were making food up here.
So we were wondering
if there was anything
we could do to help.
[ITSUKI]
Wow, awesome!
[ITSUKI, COLLETTE]
Thanks so much for coming by!
You know what? We're gonna sell
lots of bread today!
Yeah?
I sure hope you're right!
[playing, laughing]
[ITSUKI]
And still, no customers.
Tell me something. Is there some
other reason it's so dead?
[ALFIE] Everyone. You see?
This is the bakery
where our dear Visitor
has been working!
-Whoa! Look at the sweets!
-Yummy, yummy!
[CANCER]
There's crab-shaped bread!
[SCORPI]
Is there a scorpion bread?
Alfie.
What's going on?
Well, we're always training and
doing labyrinth explorations.
So, I thought
letting them see a slice
of the Visitor's
everyday life might be
a kind of fun
and educational break for them.
Think of it
as cultural immersion.
Visitor,
can I have some bread?
Me, too, I'm hungry.
Can we, Visitor?
Yeah, feel free to eat
as much as you want.
[STAR CHILDREN]
Yay!
[ALFIE]
Let's see. Here you go.
-[ITSUKI] But...
-[ALFIE] You'll owe me one.
Sound good?
You're a lifesaver.
Thank you.
[COLLETTE] I don't even think
I can remember the last time
we had this many customers
in the shop!
Guess I'll just have to go
make more bread!
Tell me more about that,
would you?
Why do you think
you have no customers?
There has to be
a good reason.
[RED] Hey.
My, my, how long do you figure
you'll keep
doing business here?
[BLUE] I can't believe you're
still wasting time baking bread.
You know it'll just go stale
on the shelf.
Who the heck are you people?
Who are we?
Are you kidding?
I'm happy to tell you
if you don't know.
We are the number one most
successful bakery in the country
and the creators
of Lunch Packs.
[COLLETTE]
Lunch Packs.
[ITSUKI]
The ones we see all the time?
Yeah! Of course the ones
you see all the time!
Our company's been looking
for prospective land
for a new storefront,
and wouldn't you know it,
this site just happens
to satisfy
every last one of our wishes
and requirements.
[RED]
So what are you waiting for?
Hurry up and hand over the shop,
already, stupids!
[BLUE] Collette,
there's really no point
in continuing to bake things
you can't sell, is there?
You should just start another
business with the money
from selling us the bakery.
-[RED] Do it.
-[BLUE] Do it.
[BOTH]
Do it! Do it! Do it!
[STAR CHILD 1]
You guys are super noisy.
We're enjoying eating
our bread, so be quiet.
[RED] Gross!
Who the heck are these kids?
[CANCER] We're not kids!
My name is Cancer.
And I'm Virgo!
Hello, little ones.
The grown-ups are trying to talk
right now,
so how 'bout you zip
your stupid lips?
No, it's you old dudes
who need to be quiet!
-Old dudes?
-[CAPRI] I mean, is scaring
nice people like this
your whole job?
Getting paid to harass
perfectly nice people
is pretty freakin' lame.
I wonder what you
old dudes' moms
and dads
would think of that!
[STAR CHILD 2]
I bet they'd probably question
whether or not
they raised you right!
[STAR CHILD 3] Sounds like
we should be pretty thankful
that the Visitor is our dad!
[SCORPI]
Yeah, and we're lucky
that Alfie is raising us, too!
[STAR CHILDREN] We're so glad
we don't have to be
big, mean adults
like these bad guys!
[RED]
Dammit! Don't you bully us!
[BLUE] This isn't over!
You can't talk to us
any way you want,
you little jerks!
[STAR CHILDREN]
Bye-bye!
They've grown strong,
haven't they?
What's amazing is,
they do nothing out of malice.
So, Collette.
Tell me, are those two jerks
the reason people
don't buy bread here?
Yes. You can buy Lunch Packs
really conveniently,
and for a very reasonable price,
so they're understandably
popular.
But because of that, most of
the other small bakeries
are going out of business.
Back when my grandpa
was still healthy,
his customers remained
very loyal to him.
But now, since they've gone,
maybe we should close.
I'm sorry, Collette.
Want a useful hint?
About what?
Lunch Pack just happens
to be a business
owned by the family of Femiruna,
the Maiden of Leo.
If you, as the Visitor,
make the request,
Femiruna may be able
to help with this!
I can take you to her
if you want!
Thanks, Mana.
Let's go.
Back as soon as I can!
[FEMIRUNA]
I do understand the problem.
Unfortunately, I'm sad to say
there's nothing I can do
that will end up helping her.
Why not? Collette,
another maiden, is in trouble!
[FEMIRUNA] I feel awful
for Collette, I really do.
But I have to let that go.
I can't let personal feelings
interfere with our operations.
[ITSUKI] Can you help me out,
personally, then?
I'm begging you!
[FEMIRUNA]
Stand up. Don't do that.
I'm sorry. I do wish
that I could help you with this,
but I just can't.
Please excuse me.
-[ITSUKI] Wait!
-Let go of me!
[ITSUKI]
Please. Just listen
to what I have
to say first, okay?
No sir, I told you
clearly to let go!
[gasping]
-[thudding]
-[whimpering]
Huh?
Femiruna?
Hey, Femiruna!
Where am I?
What is this?
How the heck did I get here?
[door opens]
[breathing heavily]
[screaming]
Stay away!
Go. Get out!
Don't you dare
get close to me!
Okay, tell me who you are,
and what it is you're planning
to do with me.
[muffled murmurs]
What? What is it
you're trying to say?
[muffled murmurs]
[whimpers]
So, how'd it go?
She still seems
to be pretty confused.
We couldn't have
a conversation at all.
From the looks of it,
I think she'd have been
even more confused
if she saw my face.
Good thing I took your advice
and used that bag.
It worked fine.
It may have been an accident,
but she did hit
her head really hard.
I know.
But do you really think
this was a good idea?
[MANA] Of course it was!
You may be Visitor,
but if you were found guilty
of hurting a maiden,
that would definitely
be a felony!
You could even be sentenced
to death!
There was really
no other option
but to escape with Femiruna
if you wanted to live!
Anyway, what's the problem?
Femiruna is safe and sound!
So, it's all for the best!
I don't know.
I'm afraid what I've done
can never really be forgiven
at this point.
[MANA]
Look, if you're feeling guilty,
all you need to do is make sure
to take good care of Femiruna!
I bet she might even
open up to you
once she senses
your sincerity.
[ITSUKI]
All right.
You have my thanks, Mana.
I've misunderstood
you all this time.
I thought you were just a dirty
little raccoon
who wanted to create
Star Children
using any disgusting
means necessary.
-I'm so sorry.
-[MANA] Don't worry about it!
But don't forget,
you should really make a point
to thank Collette, too.
After all, we'd be in a bind
if she hadn't let us borrow
the stockroom for Femiruna!
You're right. I'll do that.
So, you think I'm
a dirty raccoon
who wants to create
Star Children
using any disgusting
means necessary?
You have no idea.
I was wondering how we were
ever gonna be able to convince
Femiruna, whose guard
is literally always up,
but look how convenient
this is!
It's truly a
one-in-a-million chance!
How will it all turn out,
I wonder?
Okay. I have to
get out of this room.
[terrified cry]
No way.
Where is this place?
Itsuki.
Femiruna's bread is ready
if you want to take it to her.
Thank you.
I'll do that right now.
I sure hope
she feels better very soon.
Don't you worry.
If your bread
doesn't make her
feel better, nothing will.
-[door opens]
-[gasps]
Hey. Listen. What exactly
are you trying to achieve
by keeping me
trapped here, anyway?
[muffled speaking]
What did you say?
Am I here because
you're after my body?
No! You stay away from me!
I refuse to be tainted
by the likes of you!
[muffled murmurs, grunts]
One thing's clear. He wants me
to eat some of this bread
but I don't know why.
So, of course, now I'm wondering
what that brute
might have put in it.
I mustn't eat a single bite,
no matter what.
After all, I have
to maintain my dignity.
[stomach rumbling]
I'm not eating it,
no matter what!
[COLLETTE] You won't get better
if you don't eat.
[FEMIRUNA] I'm in charge of
my choices. I'm not eating it!
I'm in charge of my choices!
Let's see how long you
can actually keep up
that dignified lady act!
[stomach rumbling]
[door opens]
[panicked, muffled speaking]
Your threats are not
going to work on me!
Enough already!
You're the Visitor?
[ITSUKI] Why aren't you eating?
You're gonna die at this rate!
Yeah, well,
why would you care?
Listen, I know it's true
that I've hurt you,
and that it's something
that can't be undone.
I get that.
But my intention to help you
was honest, I swear.
Please believe me!
You don't have to forgive me.
But you must take far better
care of yourself from now on.
Please!
[FEMIRUNA]
This man. Look at him.
He seems genuinely concerned
about me.
Now that I think about it,
nearly every person who has
ever tried to get close to me
has only been after some piece
of my father's wealth and power.
Such intense, passionate eyes!
I've never met
anyone like him before.
It feels like he only
has eyes for me!
I'm afraid I'm feeling
too weak to move.
Do you think you could
feed me some bread?
Is that any trouble?
Of course.
Very gladly. Here.
Open your mouth.
You might need to go
a little wider.
Here it comes, ready?
Putting it in.
[coughs]
[ITSUKI] Uh-oh,
are you choking? Take it slow.
Would you stop it,
I'm not a child.
Oh, good, looks to me like you
must be all better.
Yes, I'm fine.
Now, hurry and give me
some more.
If you say so.
[FEMIRUNA]
It's delicious.
Yeah. Don't you see? That's why
I've been wanting you to try it.
Huh. You're kind of a schemer,
aren't you?
It's nothing, just ignore me.
-More bread?
-Nope. Sorry, I'm already full.
[ITSUKI]
But, you've only had two bites.
[FEMIRUNA]
I said I'm already full, okay?
All right.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Um, well...
I hope that you have
a good night.
Same to you.
Itsuki, goodnight.
[MANA] This blond lady ended up
being an easy target, after all!
When a person's placed
in a different situation
from their norm, and they spend
lots of time
with another person,
they form strong bonds!
That's what Stockholm
told me, anyway,
but who would've thought
it'd work so well!
It's really just a matter
of time, now!
You know what?
That was the very first time
that I...
Let a man touch
my bare skin.
Oh. I see.
I'm sorry.
Or, rather, it's an honor.
[FEMIRUNA]
Right!
I feel like I'm ready
to give myself to you.
I can trust you
with that, right?
[ITSUKI]
Yes, Femiruna.
Will you... have my...
Will you have my...
[muffled speaking]
Sheesh!
You're so lame, you know that?
Itsuki. I'm gonna make you
the best Star Child ever!
Well, you're being
surprisingly aggressive.
[FEMIRUNA]
Duh, of course I am!
Maiden of Leo.
What the heck did you expect?
[ITSUKI]
So, no foreplay at all?
[popping]
Just another day
with no customers.
[COLLETTE'S GRANDPA]
Collette. Collette.
Grandpa!
What are you doing here?
You should be resting!
Collette, these are for you.
Please take them.
Are those...
You're giving me
your bread recipes?
You think I should enter
the school festival
with these baked goods?
Listen, Collette.
Aim for the top.
Aim for the top, my dear.
[COLLETTE]
Grandpa.
Damn straight.
I will slay it.
[rumbling]
[door closes]
[MANA humming]
Chikuwa bread!
Abalone bread!