[MANA] It was early afternoon
on a Sunday.
Catherine,
a beautiful country girl
who was new to the big city,
was swinging her hair
with wild abandon.
"Oh, Itsuki, you're amazing,"
she gasped as he [meow]
her to climax.
I'll never forget meeting her.
It happened at a playground.
I'd been having a lot of trouble
meeting my sales quota,
just like always, and I was
sitting there on my usual bench,
when suddenly we had
that fateful encounter.
We were immediately
attracted to each other.
It was primal.
We felt no need to wait
before becoming one.
We just dove right in.
Before I knew what was
happening,
I was at her apartment.
[MANAGER]
Don't worry, no one's watching.
[PEASANT GIRL]
Please! I shouldn't!
[GOVERNOR]
Sure you should, baby.
Let me show you.
A little closer, now.
[PEASANT GIRL]
Oh, my!
[MANA]
My love.
[moaning]
[ITSUKI]
Would you give it a rest?
How long are you gonna
keep this up?
[MANA] Why, what's the problem?
Don't tell me you think
the censors will take issue
with this or something!
It's my own imagination,
after all.
I can do what I want.
No, that's not
at all what I meant.
You know exactly
what I'm talking about!
Why are all of these couples
you and me?
[MANA] What are you saying?
Are you just not interested
in kinky role-play with me?
-Tell me now!
-[ITSUKI] Would you cut it out?
-[MANA] Itsuki! More role-play!
-[ITSUKI] No!
-[MANA] Gimme, gimme, gimme!
-Stay away!
[MANA chuckles]
It's all going
according to plan.
[sighs]
Man, that was close.
[ARIE]
Hello.
Um, is there something
you're looking for?
No, to be honest,
I just happened
to come in here by accident.
It wasn't planned.
Well, that's great.
The church welcomes you,
no matter what may or may
not have brought you here.
[ITSUKI]
Right. I forgot.
You can call me Arie.
I am the maiden of Aries.
And I've devoted myself
to the church.
'Kay, so, I lied.
I was also hoping that
I might get to see you.
You mean you came all
the way here just to see me?
That's so sweet!
-[footsteps, giggling]
-[CHILDREN] Arie!
I can't figure out
my homework!
[BOY 1]
I'm so hungry, Arie!
[GIRL 2]
Me, too, me, too. I want snacks!
[ITSUKI]
You have kids?
They're not mine.
I take care of several of
the children around here
and sometimes help them
with their schoolwork.
Arie, I'm hungry!
[GIRL 2]
Hurry up, come on!
Patience.
We have a special guest.
Don't mind me.
I'll come back another time.
[MANA]
Good work, Itsuki!
Look at you, bonding right off
the bat with our dear Arie!
Way to go!
[chattering]
Are you about done
in there, Itsuki?
Sorry, I'm in line, but
these hungry people are nuts!
-[yelling]
-[MAHIRU sighs]
Fine.
I'll just wait for you outside.
[Itsuki grunting]
Ouch, that actually hurt.
On top of that,
these are all I got to buy.
[gasps]
Hey, wait!
How did I lose her?
What should I do?
I mean, why in the world
was I chosen
to be one of the maidens,
anyway?
[ITSUKI]
What was her name?
Yuzuha?
Is that right?
I wonder if she was able
to get anything for lunch.
[grunts]
What the hell was that?
[MANA snickering]
Give me a break, Mana.
What do you want?
[MANA] I bet I know
exactly what you're thinking
out here by yourself.
Master Pervert Baron's
Erotic Stories, Volume Two!
Just like in the "Seductive
Badass Housewife" chapter,
I bet you're hoping
for a hot MILF
to show up with a whip
in one hand
and a perfectly completed tax
form in the other, aren't you?
-Aren't you?
-[ITSUKI sighs]
So, this is where
you get that crap from.
[MANA] Now, granted, the stories
written by my beloved
Master Pervert Baron
may have ever-so-slightly
dated settings for Sola,
but they should still be
pretty useful, I would think.
Hmm, which setting
would be good for Arie?
The really pure,
conservative women like her
tend to be
pretty darn guarded.
-Really? And is she?
-[MANA chuckles]
[MANA]
Is that a note of interest
I hear in your voice,
you little perv?
Look, you don't have to worry
one little bit!
I'm telling you,
Master Pervert Baron's stories
cover a wide range
of situations!
Short story number eighteen,
"I'll Have Your Fig as Thanks
for the Present"
might be particularly
useful for you!
The story is,
in order for him
to obtain her [boing] fig,
the protagonist is very crafty
and gives her a present
she loves,
so, then, of course,
she falls for him!
Because, presents!
So, hurry, go talk to her
and find out specifically
what kind of present
she might like!
Get that [boing]!
I believe in you, Itsuki!
Hey, where'd you go?
[knocks]
[sighs]
[door unlocks]
[ITSUKI]
Oh, right.
Here. [gasps]
Hey, you don't have to worry.
I only came by to bring you
something to eat.
Here. A sandwich.
It looked like you didn't
get to buy one
because it was so crowded.
Sandwich?
Yeah, I just happened
to buy two.
Anyway, here.
With no filling?
[ITSUKI]
Sorry, yeah.
These are all I could grab.
Actually, that's kind of great.
Thank you so much,
because now I can erase it.
Erase what?
[YUZUHA] See?
You use it like this.
[ITSUKI]
Oh, wow.
[YUZUHA]
Bread can be used as a food,
or as an eraser.
It's really very convenient.
Cool. I'm glad there was
no filling, then.
Me, too. Plain bread
is actually my favorite.
Even though I know
it's kinda weird.
Well, aside from onigiri,
which is my all-time favorite.
-Look at you.
-[YUZUHA] Hmm?
[ITSUKI]
You're smiling now.
It seemed like you were
a little afraid of me before.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Please forgive me.
No, you have nothing
to apologize for!
You know what else I did?
This is terrible,
but I completely forgot
to greet you!
So, um, I guess I...
Here I am, greeting you!
Hello, there.
Uh...
I'm Yuzuha!
It's nice to meet you,
kindred soul.
[chuckles]
Kindred soul?
[laughs]
[MANA]
She said, "I'll pour some tea,"
as she shook his tightly
clenched hand with hers.
She went to the kitchen.
The water was boiling
in the kettle.
However, however, she felt like
she was the one
who was all steamy
and boiling inside!
The uncontrollable,
burning lust.
"I can't hold it any longer!
"Please, drink some of the
hot tea I just made!
"Swallow it with your mouth!
"Yeah, that's it!"
[slurps]
Is the tea okay?
Do you need anything?
No, it's really good.
-I bet it's not really.
-Huh?
Well, it's just...
I'm pretty sure my tea
isn't actually good.
I mean, I don't even
want to drink it, myself.
No, I genuinely like it!
And I don't lie about tea.
So, thank you, Yuzuha.
I'm so, so sorry.
Wait, what are you
apologizing for, now?
Something else.
This one is for calling you
a kindred soul without bothering
to explain what I meant by that.
It just popped right out
of my mouth
without even thinking about it.
Hey, please don't stress.
It was a compliment,
and I took it as such.
Good to hear.
I'm so glad, kindred soul.
So, tell me, Yuzuha,
what kind of paintings
have you been working on?
You said you like to paint.
Isn't that right?
It's not so much
that I like it.
-It's just my job.
-Oh, really?
-Cool.
-Yes. So, unfortunately,
I have to go
back and forth between here
and the academy
twice a day, every day.
I don't really want
to go outside
but what are you gonna do,
I guess.
You don't like being
around people?
The truth is, I started
confining myself long before
I was even chosen
to be a maiden.
For instance, when I sleep
and when I dream
I'm always in a box.
That's where I've always felt
the safest in the whole world.
So, then is the box
you're referring to,
the one right there?
You think I'm insanely weird,
don't you?
Well, that is a coffin, right?
Yes.
I gave it a name
so it might be
a little more palatable.
Katarine,
the coffin.
Wow, it's got a good ring.
But, doesn't one usually
put dead people in a coffin?
I know, but it's just
such a perfect fit for me.
I sleep so peacefully
inside a coffin.
I have very vivid dreams, too,
where I travel to all
different kinds of places.
You see, my job is to paint
the things I see
in my dreams each night.
I sure can't seem to sell any,
though.
Is that why you don't
go outside very often?
Yes, because I'm able to see
so many wondrous things
without going outside.
Actually, to be precise,
I used to see them.
Is there
something wrong, Yuzuha?
No. I'm okay.
I just haven't had any dreams
at all for a while, now.
[gasps]
I guess you might say I've kind
of lost my inspiration.
Maybe it's just what they call
a "slump."
But I'm worried.
If this goes on,
I'm afraid that
I might have to give up my job.
That's rough. Hey, why don't we
go spend a little time outside?
You have to refresh your mind
once in a while.
I know, but I really
don't wanna go out there.
I've got it!
How about if I go and buy us
a few more sandwiches?
No filling, of course.
And then, we can go to the park
tomorrow and eat them together.
There shouldn't be
too many people around,
and it's close by.
Does that sound okay?
More than okay.
I wonder if I bought too much.
[MANA] I was so sure
you were going after Arie.
But your sights are already set
on another girl, aren't they?
You've got [bleep] of brass,
don't you, mister?
I guess I should really expect
nothing less from the guy
who just slayed
the Double Love Ritual, huh?
Oh, stop,
it's nothing like that.
Look, just try not to get
in my way today, okay?
[MANA]
Someone's a little jumpy!
You must really be looking
forward to this!
You're the real
Master Pervert Baron!
[ITSUKI] Enough with that
something-something Baron crap!
Leave me alone! Please!
[MANA] Well, in that case,
I'll just have to enjoy this
in a voyeuristic,
peeping role-play kind of way!
[ITSUKI] Stop talking
and get the hell outta here!
Shoo! Go on, shoo!
[sighs heavily]
-[YUZUHA] Oh, kindred soul!
-[ITSUKI] Huh?
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me
for being so late.
[gasping]
Thanks for waiting.
The sandwiches you bought
for me are so yummy!
-I can't get enough!
-Cool. I'm glad to hear it.
So, what made you bring
your coffin with you?
And why does it look a bit
different than yesterday?
I'm actually
impressed you noticed.
I made some cute decorations
for today,
because it seemed
kind of special.
What do you think of them?
Oh, uh, gosh.
How would I describe that?
I guess I would say that
it looks very feminine.
That's correct!
That was my concept.
You saw it and you
understood it,
which means you understand me.
Really?
I was right?
Yeah, coffins can have
kind of a masculine quality,
so I thought it might be cute
if I made mine girlier.
Sure, that makes sense.
You know, talking
is my least favorite thing
and it's such a relief
to hang out with someone
who doesn't need
everything explained.
I really wish more people
were like you, Itsuki.
I think I should
probably point out
that we've been talking
pretty well this whole time.
Well, yeah, and that's
because you're yourself.
Hmm, I wonder why I'm so
comfortable talking with you.
I guess it really doesn't
matter, though, right?
[MANA]
Damn you, Itsuki.
When did you learn
about coffin role-play?
You've become
a high-level player
in such an impressively
short amount of time!
So, is there anything
inside the coffin?
It looked like it was
really heavy.
Well, I brought some
painting supplies.
[ITSUKI]
I see that.
[YUZUHA] Coffins are actually
very convenient for trips.
You can sleep in them,
obviously,
and you can haul things
around like a backpack.
Wow, that does
sound pretty handy.
Although, I'm not really sure
why I brought the paint supplies
since I know
I can't paint today, anyway.
You mean you didn't
dream last night?
[ITSUKI]
I see.
But, you know, you can paint
even if you don't dream.
Come on. Take a look.
Isn't it beautiful?
You're so right!
[MANA cheeping]
Hey, what's wrong,
are you okay?
Yeah! Sure!
I'm totally fine!
But what do you think
about taking
a long walk
over that way?
'Course. I think I'd go
anywhere with you.
[ITSUKI] Oh, I'll carry that.
Isn't it heavy?
No, it's fine.
I made this thing light
so it'd be easy to carry.
But thank you for asking,
Itsuki.
I wish there was something
I could give you
to repay your kindness.
I don't need anything in return.
But, I...
Hey, Mom, look over there.
What's that?
[MOTHER gasps]
Don't look, honey!
What?
But why not?
Sweetheart,
just stop pointing at it!
Come on, we're leaving!
[DAUGHTER]
But what is it doing?
[gasps]
Hey, listen.
I'm gonna go. See you later.
[ITSUKI]
Wait! Don't leave!
I never should've come.
I know better
than to go outside.
[ITSUKI] No, Yuzuha,
it's so great that you came!
They weren't talking about you!
I don't care.
All I know is,
I wouldn't have
gotten humiliated
if I'd just stayed at home
where it's safe for me.
Yuzuha!
[MANA]
What's the matter over here?
It's your fault!
It's all your fault!
[MANA]
What?
[YUZUHA] I'm so sorry,
sweet kindred soul.
You were there with me,
and they saw that.
So now, they probably think
you're a weirdo, too.
Forgive me!
[ITSUKI]
Lord. Help me.
I think somehow I hurt
Yuzuha's feelings today.
How can I fix it?
What can I do that will help
her feel better?
[ARIE] I think Yuzuha
walks a hard road.
From what I hear,
she's been frail since birth.
Is it some kind of illness?
Well, I don't know
if you have this in Sola,
but her condition is called
sleep sickness here,
in our world.
Sleep sickness?
[ARIE] Yes.
She burns away a bit of her life
every time she sleeps.
So, when she does,
her life gets shorter.
Those with the illness
don't live very long,
and there's nothing
to do for them.
So sad.
And there's really no cure?
Mm-mm. No, unfortunately,
no one has discovered
an effective treatment.
Thankfully, there's no pain
involved, though,
which is a blessing.
Death will arrive for her
while she sleeps.
She'll simply never
wake up again.
It may be the most peaceful
death one could ask for.
Itsuki.
Did Yuzuha happen to tell you
why she carries
that coffin around with her
everywhere she goes?
Yeah, she said
it makes her feel safe.
It's really for the benefit
of others, though.
She doesn't want her death
to be any trouble.
She wants it to be easy
for those around her.
That's just who she is.
I have a feeling
that's also why
Yuzuha keeps to herself
as much as she does.
So she's not a burden.
It's so unfair.
She's done nothing
to deserve this.
Why?
Listen to me.
Itsuki, all you need to do
is keep supporting her.
I have a strong feeling
Yuzuha hasn't quite given up
on life just yet.
I'm sure your presence
must give her hope.
So just keep showing
her kindness.
[hammering]
Whatcha doin', Mana?
[MANA]
Itsuki! You're back!
I'm really sorry about earlier.
It's all right.
What are you up to
with all this, though?
[MANA] I'm building you a coffin
as an apology.
See, you can put this
beside her coffin and then
it'll be a double coffin
instead of a double bed!
-So you can make up using--
-Mana, great work!
[ITSUKI]
Yuzuha. Yuzuha!
You're in there. Open the door.
Come on!
Yuzuha!
If you don't open this door,
I'm gonna have to break it down.
Is that really what you want?
No!
Please don't do that.
Oh.
Good, let's go for a walk!
No, I'm sorry,
I really can't go with you.
Please forgive me.
[ITSUKI] Wait!
Just take a look at this, okay?
It's Kanda, the coffin!
He's a new friend
for your Katarine!
And, of course, I brought
some sandwiches, too.
Don't worry.
If you can't see beauty
because you can't dream,
then see the world with me!
I can give you a tour
of the beautiful outdoors!
I want to see it, too, with you.
And I promise to hold you
if it ever gets scary.
I just want to be able
to spend time with you, Yuzuha.
Do you really?
[ITSUKI]
Come on. Let's go.
Okay.
-[splashing]
-[both laughing]
[YUZUHA] It's still bright,
so I guess I can't see it.
I was trying to figure out
where my constellation is.
Your constellation's
Pisces, right?
Yes, and it's the faintest
constellation
in the whole zodiac, which seems
pretty fitting, doesn't it?
That's so Yuzuha.
The shape is very irregular
and uneven,
so it just doesn't stand out
like some of the others.
Standing out and being bright
doesn't always make things
better, you know?
Well, if I'm honest,
being bright
and standing out
isn't very me, anyway.
But I wonder, why is Pisces
considered part of the zodiac
when it doesn't even have
any third-magnitude stars?
It's a Piece of the PIE-cies.
That's a pun bomb.
Wow, I guess you're really
full of sur-Pisces,
aren't you?
D'oh! Pun bomb.
[BOTH laugh]
Seriously,
remember,
Pisces was included
because someone found it.
I guess that's true.
Someone must have seen it
up there.
Yeah.
[YUZUHA] So, there are people
who can recognize it
even though it doesn't
stand out, huh?
Thank you for that,
kindred soul.
Would you like to hear
my theory about you?
I think at least half of you
is made up of pure kindness.
I'm feeling sleepy,
all of a sudden.
Think I'll take a nap.
You sleep well, Yuzuha.
[YUZUHA]
Is this a dream?
It feels so gentle and warm,
and perfect.
I feel so safe.
[ITSUKI]
Huh? You had a dream?
It was a big sur-Pisces
for me, too.
-'Cause I'm a Pisces.
-'Cause you're a Pisces.
[both laughing]
I wanna do something for you.
I know you don't want anything,
as thanks for all your kindness
towards me,
but I really want to give you
something back, anyway.
Oh, please don't worry about it.
You don't get it.
I'm saying...
I think I can actually
fulfill my duty
as maiden as long
as it's with you.
Not because it's my job,
or 'cause I've given up on life.
I just really want to connect
with you that way.
You're absolutely sure?
You're really willing
to have my child?
[MANA] Master Pervert Baron,
we owe this moment all to you!
Your novels are
the gospel truth!
[YUZUHA]
I'm nervous.
Don't be.
Just follow my lead, okay?
I trust you to be gentle.
[laughing]
[shimmering]
[energy bursting]
[popping]
[MANA] ♪ Mango, fig,
cherries, and berries ♪
♪ Ripe for the picking,
Ripe for the picking! ♪
What in the heck
are you singing?
[MANA]
Are you kidding right now?
It's the erotica fruits song,
sung by Prince Dandy!
Come on, sing it with me and
awaken your virility, Itsuki!
Huh? What happened
to something-Baron?
[MANA]
Naturally, I finished reading
all of Master Pervert
Baron's novels.
The next pervert is super
erotica musician, Prince Dandy!
[sighs]
[MANA]
Also, I have something for you.
[ITSUKI]
A present? For me?
[MANA]
Why would I give you a present?
No!
It's for Arie, silly!
Take this and rush to her side,
immediately!
You can have an erotica
fruits parade!
♪ Mango, fig, cherries,
and berries ♪
♪ Ripe for the picking
Ripe for the picking ♪
Hey, Arie?
Guess she's not here today.
-Arie!
-[gasps]
[ITSUKI] Wow, I didn't know
there was a room there.
Oh, hello there!
So, I've heard congratulations
are in order,
that you performed with Yuzuha
without any issues.
Yeah!
All thanks to you, I think.
I didn't do anything.
Oh, my, could that present
be for me?
Well, yeah, this is...
just... Here you go.
Gosh, what a surprise!
Thank you so much.
Yeah, of course.
You gave me such
wonderful advice.
Crap. Just realized I forgot
to check what was inside.
Hope it's okay.
[ARIE]
Wow. There's so much!
How nice.
I'm impressed, Itsuki.
I'm not sure how,
but you obviously
understand me very well.
-[whipping]
-[Itsuki yelling]
[ITSUKI] Is this the role-play
from the OP?
More!
Gimme more!
[MANA]
Who would've thought Arie
would enjoy that type of thing
so much!
Mana, are you absolutely sure
you want to be
tied up like this?
[MANA]
Oh yeah, this is good.
Things are getting
really interesting, actually.
Come on, sing with me, Mahiru.
You, too, you little perv
sitting in front of the TV!
[BOTH] ♪ Mango, fig,
cherries and berries ♪
♪ Ripe for the picking
Ripe for the picking ♪
[MANA singing]
Naginata?