[yells]
[crumbling]
[screams]
[cheering]
That was a close one,
but, wonderful job, Itsuki!
Now it’s time to offer up
the Star Ward!
[ITSUKI] We’re finally a quarter
of the way there.
[clears throat]
That’s absolutely correct!
The next foes we’re
going to meet
lie a bit deeper
within the labyrinth.
-Does that mean--
-[MANA] The deeper you go,
the more concentrated and evil
the Impurities will become.
-Yup.
-That doesn’t seem good.
[MONSTER roars]
[rumbling]
Huh? Hey, Visitor!
Not again.
[MANA]
Such an unsettling roar.
So, what’s causing it?
Do we still not know?
[MANA]
Sorry.
But honestly,
no matter what it is,
you have no chance
of winning against it
unless you increase the number
of Star Children, fast!
I know.
It’s been a problem.
We’ve been fighting
so much lately
that I haven’t had time
to see the maidens.
[MANA laughs lecherously]
Oh, yes.
I know.
Believe me!
That’s why I’ve prepared
a special event
which will give you a rest
and hopefully close the distance
between you
and those dear lovelies!
That’s not possible.
[MANA]
A summer fling!
If you’re on a resort vacation,
you can do it any time,
any place!
Anything goes!
Hello.
Attention, passengers.
I want you to know that today
is totally my treat!
Your only job is
to enjoy yourselves!
[applause and laughter]
-[RUKA] Great!
-[FEMIRUNA] My favorite!
Yay for free trips!
You’ve outdone yourself, Mana.
Wow, I never realized
you were so giving.
[MANA]
That’s because I’m not!
This is all for the sake
of the Love Rituals,
of course, you silly boy.
You must be so happy.
Twelve half-naked maidens
are about to be ready
and willing to play with you,
day or night,
-you lucky perv!
-Huh?
[screeches] You imbecile!
Do you really still not get it?
I’m setting you up
for some hook-ups!
I mean, duh!
You’re going to the beach
for a summer fling!
Get a taste of some real,
raunchy freedom under the sun
with twelve hot, single,
and-ready-to-mingle maidens!
[MAHIRU]
Did you hear, girls?
Mana just said he even
picked out swimsuits
for each of us to wear.
[ITSUKI]
Really? That’s great.
[SEIYA] Hey, pretty ladies!
How’s it goin’?
Oh, Liris, it’s you!
What a coincidence!
How funny is this?
I’m heading to the beach, too,
for a photo shoot!
Did that guy not finish
getting dressed?
[CANCER]
He’s creepy if you ask me.
[STARCHILD]
He looks very weak.
[SCORPI] I bet I could beat him
with one blow!
Who’s that?
[MANA]
You really don’t know?
He’s Seiya, the idol
of the whole academy.
Very popular with the girls.
Ugh!
He’s so persistent!
Seiya’s been approaching
each of us maidens, one by one.
It’s like he’s some kind of
weird, maiden-obsessed stalker.
Sounds about right.
He used to come up and drink
at the bar where I work
every single night.
And before that,
he was following me around,
but now his target
seems to be Liris.
Are you serious?
[LIRIS]
I don’t really think
he’s some kind of
bad person, though.
Huh? Why not?
[LIRIS]
It’s his nature.
He’s a playboy by birth,
there’s no doubt.
His personality makes him
pursue maidens
who would never fall for him
in a million years.
The only thing
for any of us to do
is to wait until he gives up.
Hold on, how did he find out
we were going
to the beach, anyway?
What’s the matter?
Who? Me?
Nothing. It’s really nothing.
[MANA]
I’m really sorry!
♪
[GIRLS laughing]
[giggling]
[grunts]
[MANA]
Hey, Itsuki!
How do like the swimsuits
I picked out? Good?
They’re so sexy I bet you can
barely resist them, can you?
[MANA giggling]
If I really wanna know
how excited you are...
Quit that!
Would you stop?
It’s plenty thick!
[MANA screams]
We came all the way
to the beach.
Not gonna swim?
My fortune today said
I should stay away from water.
[ITSUKI] Do you mind
if I sit with you?
[gasp] Are you sure
you wanna do that?
I’m pretty boring, you should
hang with everyone else!
[ALFIE]
Swing those arms!
-C’mon! Pick up the pace!
-[camera shutter clicking]
[ITSUKI]
His “photo shoot” was selfies?
Yeah, he’s basically
a textbook narcissist.
Don’t feel like you have
to defend his behavior.
I’m not.
I’m telling you,
it’s all from
my fortune-telling.
So, um,
what exactly would you
like to know?
My fated soul-mate.
Who’s out there for me?
[LIRIS]
Huh? Well, uh...
[chuckles] I already know.
Maidens have to be virgins.
But that just means they have
to remain pure, right?
So, even though their duty
is important,
they’re still free
to fall in love, aren’t they?
[LIRIS]
I think he might officially be
the biggest narcissist
that ever existed.
I fear there is literally no one
who can help him now.
Are you sure?
That seems a bit dramatic.
What’re you saying?
Are you implying that
my fortune-telling is a sham
and doesn’t mean anything?
No! That’s not
what I meant at all!
Why? Why’re you
being so mean?
[ITSUKI]
Oh, no! Oh, crap! I’m sorry!
[LIRIE]
Hey, you bastard!
What the hell
did you do to Liris?
What? Nothing!
Who’re you?
I’m Lirie!
Yep, my chest is very tight,
and I’m on the verge of tears.
So, what did you do?
[ITSUKI gasps]
I was just saying
that maybe she shouldn’t put so
much faith in fortune-telling.
Unforgivable!
Were you trying to mock her?
Come on, I mean,
it’s just fortune-telling!
Just? Really?
Are you crazy?
Liris has a true gift.
She’s never been wrong!
Every word she says is always
a hundred percent accurate!
No way, that’s impossible.
-Cool. Then why
don’t you go ahead
and tell me exactly when,
where and what time she got
it wrong, and I’ll concede!
Well?
Cat got your tongue or what?
Listen.
Forgive me.
But, I--
I don’t believe.
Not in fortune-telling, anyway.
You’re a fool!
Soon enough, you’ll see it
for yourself
and then you’ll change your
tune, you nitwitted simpleton.
Okay, Liris.
Tell this stupid Visitor
his fortune.
Show him that you’re
the real deal!
Come on!
[LIRIS]
That actually hurts.
Are you all right?
Tell me this.
Was Lirie just upset?
[ITSUKI] Yeah, she told me
that I should let you
tell me my fortune first,
and then I can decide
if I believe in it or not.
[LIRIS] I’d like to ask you
to keep an open mind, as well.
If you can do that, I think
you’ll understand, in time.
Sure, I guess.
I’ll try to, if that will make
both of you happy.
Okay, please allow me to look.
[gasps]
What is it?
What’s wrong?
I’m sorry, it’s nothing.
What did you see?
Well, um...
I, uh...
Not really sure.
Actually, you were
totally right to begin with.
My fortune-telling is a sham.
That’s fine.
This is fine!
I’m sorry.
I can’t do this.
[LIRIS crying]
[SEIYA]
Hey, what do you think?
What could those two
be arguing about?
[MANA] How should I know?
I have no idea.
Gonna reward you for this.
[MANA]
Grin!
Did you make Liris
feel crappy again?
That wasn’t my intention.
I just had her read my fortune,
like you said.
[LIRIE]
So, what was it?
-The result of the reading!
-Huh?
[LIRIE]
Wait a second.
Does this mean
that you believe her now
or are you still
being stupid?
But I--
-[MANA] Whisper, whisper...
-Ah, a lover’s quarrel.
That’s kind of adorable.
Give me what you promised!
Right.
Very well done, Mana.
[MANA squeals happily]
-What is that?
-Just shut up and keep quiet!
[scoffs]
So, that’s what happened.
‘Kay, Visitor.
Are you ready
for what comes next?
[ITSUKI]
Uh, why? What’s next?
How can you be
this freakin’ dumb?
I’m about to tell you
what Liris couldn’t bear
to say herself.
Beware!
You will die at this rate!
Where the hell
did that come from?
[LIRIE] She saw the seal
of death on you.
It’s gonna happen
in the near-future, too.
Well, that sucks.
Would you stop?
Take this seriously, please!
Do you really still
not believe her?
Listen, there’s nothing I can
do if that’s my fortune, right?
I mean, come on,
how’m I s’posed to react?
[scoffs] I know.
What if you
dropped dead right here?
Look, I want you to remember
we gave you
a proper warning, you got it?
Yeah, sure, okay.
[LIRIE] How dare you act
so blasé about this!
Damn it, you drive me crazy!
[whines] That hurts.
How am I supposed
to believe any of this stuff?
[LIRIS]
Um, Itsuki, did she...?
Yeah. Lirie told me everything.
[ITSUKI] Sorry, I don’t mean
to insult you,
but I still don’t believe it.
But you have to,
because it’s the truth!
Okay, then exactly when, where,
and how am I going to die?
I mean, if your skills are
absolute, then just tell me.
[LIRIS] Please don’t take
this attitude about it!
A maiden’s duty is to be of
assistance to the Visitor!
Yes, fortune-telling is often
used to predict the future,
but it can also be used
to avoid any danger!
The thing is, though,
you’ll have to truly believe
in my powers in order
to get the very best results.
Look over there for me,
would you?
Remember, how I told you
I didn’t think it was possible
to stop him earlier?
Well, now I think I can change
his behavior
using the results
of my fortune-telling!
[ITSUKI]
You mean...
I can’t let anything bad
happen to the maidens, so,
I sent his worst mortal weakness
over there, just in case.
[MANA] This is Madam Tokugawa’s
special formula.
It can make anyone climax
right on the spot
with just a fingertip’s worth!
It’s incredible!
I call it Mana’s Touch!
[SEIYA moans passionately]
[MANA]
Now, the finishing blow!
Hang on tight!
Mana, Mana, Mana, Mana, Mana,
Mana, Mana, Mana, Mana, Mana...
[SEIYA moaning passionately]
[MANA]
The fun has just begun!
[SEIYA]
If you touch right there,
-it’s so good.
-[thudding]
Don’t stop!
[SEIYA moans passionately]
[MANA]
My work here is done.
I’ve brought joy
to the world. Twice.
Well, I guess
one thing’s for sure.
Seiya certainly won’t be
bothering anyone else
for quite some time.
You really did manage
to change fate, huh?
Do you think so?
Are you saying you might
actually believe
in my fortune-telling now,
Itsuki?
About before...
I’m sorry if I made
you feel badly.
I really want to
'believe you now!
-Should we?
-Yes, we should.
[mystical humming]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
You all right?
It’s, uh...
I’m just...
I’m gonna leave
the rest of this to Lirie
-if that’s okay with you!
-[MANA cackles]
♪
Wait a second!
This feels a little too sudden!
What the heck happened?
[LIRIE]
Apparently...
Your life will be spared if
we make a Star Child right now.
Whoa, that’s fascinating.
But are you really sure?
[LIRIE] Liris’s fortune-telling
is absolute.
Anyway, you believe
in our power, don’t you?
Yeah.
I do.
So, will you please
have my Star Child?
-[LIRIE] I’ve got no choice.
-[LIRIS] I’ll do my very best!
[indistinct groaning]
I can’t hold on any more!
I give up!
If one of you falls,
all of you will pay!
Way too cruel!
Sometimes, I think
she’s really a demon.
You two, over there!
You better focus harder
if you have the energy to chat!
Hey, guys!
Everyone training hard today?
[KIDS gasp]
Hi, Visitor!
Oh, Itsuki!
What a wonderful surprise!
I wasn’t expecting to see you
at all today!
You could’ve told me
you were coming,
you know,
you bad thing, you!
-[ALFIE giggles]
-[BOTH] Stare.
Um, would you like tea?
I figured you might stop
by sometime
so I ordered
some to have on hand
from the “Café
with the Great Red Tea!”
Oh. Okay, then.
Ah, it’s really good!
[MANA] Would you like to
check out this yumminess?
Then check it out here,
on the website!
I’m glad you liked it!
-[branches rustling]
-Who’s that?
Oh, great!
Now he’s after Arie?
Hey, Seiya!
Enough is enough!
He is so hot!
Welp, he found me,
time to go.
[ITSUKI panting]
Arie, you okay?
Oh! No, I’m not Arie!
You must’ve mistaken me
for someone else!
I’m so sorry!
Bye, now!
Huh?
Hey, Seiya, wait up!
[panting]
I don’t understand.
How did he know it was me?
I put on a disguise
and everything!
[SMITH]
Welcome.
[ARIE] Hello, is the item
I ordered finished yet?
It is, sorry
to keep you waiting.
It was quite a task,
I’ll tell you.
I can’t get over
the beauty of this steel!
The dark reflection is so deep
that it reminds me of a jewel.
[SMITH] Ah, there’s only one
blacksmith left in Granvania
who can polish steel
like that.
But why did you want
such an old-fashioned weapon?
We maidens cannot fight,
and that can be
very difficult to accept.
So, I figure, at least,
I can feel close to Itsuki,
if I keep mindful
with this naginata by my side.
[chuckling]
If only I could find myself
a wife just like you, Arie!
Nah, you don’t
really mean that.
Oh my gosh!
I lost track of time
and the kids will be back
at the church soon!
[footsteps]
Welcome home, darling.
My sweet, little naginata.
[panting]
[ARIE]
Lord.
Thank you for protecting
Itsuki again today.
I am forever grateful.
-[door slams]
-Huh?
Hello?
Who’s there, please?
[panting]
Hi, again.
Do you mind if I hide out here?
The God I serve says
to love your enemies,
and even pray for those
who persecute you.
You’re welcome here.
Thank you for that.
Is there something
troubling you?
I’d be happy to listen, if you
think it would help you at all.
[ARIE]
I understand.
Remember, love is patient,
and it’s always kind.
I can see all the love
that you have inside.
I hope it all works out
very soon.
Thank you so much, Arie!
It’s been so painful
not being able to tell anyone!
I truly understand.
And now, you’ve been
so vulnerable
in sharing your secret with me.
I’d like to share mine,
but only if it would be
all right with you.
[SEIYA breathing heavily
-[wood creaking]
-[ARIE giggling]
[ARIE]
Yes! Like that!
But could you maybe do it
a little harder?
You mean, kinda like this?
No, harder!
Please!
Even harder!
Okay, well,
then how about this?
Are you kidding me
with that? Stop!
Quit playing around
and try using a proper stance!
Um, to be honest,
this thing is kinda
surprisingly heavy for me.
[ARIE]
What’re you trying to say?
You’re being mean!
You’re making Naginata cry!
[gasping]
-[SEIYA screams]
-[ARIE screams]
[ARIE]
No! Help! Please!
Arie!
Are you okay?
-[gasps] Seiya, you bastard!
-[SEIYA exclaims]
Get the hell off her!
[SEIYA] No, listen!
It’s not like that, Itsuki!
Shut up!
Not a word!
There’s a deep and kind of
complicated
explanation for this.
[ITSUKI]
I don’t want excuses! Shut up!
I’m so relieved!
Itsuki, wait!
[ARIE]
We were just playing around.
It wasn’t anything.
Arie, don’t worry.
I’ll never tell another soul
about this.
I swear.
Not even if you’ve lost
your status as a maiden.
-[bell ringing]
-[MANA exclaims]
[MANA]
No worries there, Itsuki!
She’s still giving off
the very distinct aroma
of a fresh, untouched virgin.
In fact,
get this!
She’s still an innocent maiden
who hasn’t even experienced
her first kiss yet!
What exactly is
going on then, Arie?
[ITSUKI gasps]
What is this?
Yeah, I know,
it’s a little creepy, isn’t it?
That’s fine.
I knew you’d react this way.
This is awesome!
I’m amazed you were able
to collect so many!
-[ITSUKI gasps]
-[ARIE giggles]
With that, you have to
point it down in a stance.
Well, do it!
-Oh, uh, kinda like this?
-[ARIE gasps]
Yes! Oh God, that’s wonderful!
That particular pose makes
the long spear glitter
more than any weapon
I’ve ever seen!
Look, the aura at the spike
is the proof that
it’s happy in your hands!
Do you feel it?
You are the chosen one!
Oh, wow?
-You really believe that?
-Hey, Seiya!
Don’t just stand there!
Take a photo!
We may never get
this chance again!
[SEIYA] Living for it!
Just leave it to me!
You really are
super weird, man.
-Itsuki, try this next.
-[camera shutter clicking]
Now, this is just my personal
opinion, of course,
but I think a bow
is most erotic
when the bowstring is stretched
to its absolute limit!
The tension it releases
is just out of this world!
[ITSUKI]
Right.
Why don’t you try it?
Whoo! Gimme more!
You really are
something else, aren’t you?
You’re just so strong,
I don’t even think
I’m strong enough
-to pull that hard.
-[bow twangs]
[gasps] Did you just hear that?
How happy she sounds?
She’s singing in pure elation!
[ITSUKI]
Uh, Arie, aren’t we finished?
[ARIE] Not yet!
Just a little longer!
[ITSUKI]
Seriously?
Good, Itsuki! Gimme more!
Gimme more!
Weapons are all beautiful,
but they shine to their fullest
when they’re in the hands
of a great Visitor!
I truly do believe that!
Don’t worry, loves.
I know just how you all feel.
I really do.
You want to be fully embraced
by Itsuki,
our Visitor, don’t you?
But I’m so sorry,
‘cause you see,
I think I’m finally ready
to go next!
[MANA]
Oh, Arie, you perv!
-Love it!
-[ARIE] Oh, no!
Wait a minute,
what am I thinking?
[ITSUKI] So, is this what
you were doing earlier?
Yes. I asked Seiya
to hold her for me,
but as it ended up,
he unfortunately
couldn’t handle her.
[ITSUKI]
Uh, what’s that?
It’s the ceremonial weapon
for weddings.
A naginata.
When the time comes,
I want her by my side for ours.
Wait, what?
Arie, I think you might have
this whole thing all wrong.
-Huh?
-[MANA] I hate to tell you,
but the real naginatas
actually look like this.
[ARIE]
No way!
[MANA] There’s also the Firearms
and Swords Control Act.
You’d be arrested on site for
carrying something as dangerous
as that around Sola!
What?
That’s so sad.
Then...
does that mean that I’ve done
all of this in vain?
I dunno.
I’m actually relieved.
Huh?
[ARIE] Before I thought
you were kind of intimidating
and hard to approach
because you seemed so serious.
-Oh, no.
-But then...
I got to see this side.
The side of you that gets
excited about things,
and it’s great.
Does that mean
that you’re considering...?
[ITSUKI] Yes, I’m starting
to like you a lot,
and I hope you like me, too.
Itsuki!
Please don’t cry.
I can’t help it.
I’m so happy!
Then, can we...?
Arie, will you please consent
to have my child?
Of course, I will!
♪
You know, it’s funny.
I’m so nervous, now that
it’s the real thing.
Don’t worry,
I was nervous, too.
Just come in
when you feel ready.
-No rush at all.
-[ARIE] Okay.
Oh, Itsuki, you’re so sweet,
but I do wonder
if you already guessed
my little secret
a long time ago.
[whip cracks]
[ITSUKI groans]
[ITSUKI]
What?
[ARIE laughs]
-[whip smacks]
-[ITSUKI grunts]
-[whip smacking]
-[ITSUKI grunting]
-[smacking continues]
-[grunting continues]
[ITSUKI yells]
[breathing heavily]
-[whip smacks]
-[ITSUKI yelps]
[ARIE] Thank you so much
for waiting, Seiya.
Yeah, sure. Hi.
So, did the Love Ritual
end up going well?
Yes! It did.
[SEIYA]
You lucky thing.
I’m so jealous.
But I did get some great photos,
thanks to you,
so I guess we’re even.
Here you go.
[ARIE giggles]
This is wonderful!
What about the rest of ‘em?
You mean from
the trip. Right?
-Yes, the trip.
-[SEIYA] Aren’t they great?
[ARIE] Yes.
You do really excellent work!
Thank you!
Maybe I’ll make an exception
to my rule, for once,
and let you see
my favorite shot!
[ARIE gasps]
[BOTH]
It's so cute!
-[wind blows]
-[SEIYA gasps]
[MANA gasps]
[exclaims]
[MANA] So, Seiya is actually
after Itsuki?
[MANA humming]
[MANA]
Hoodlum.