-[footsteps]
-[panting]
-[grunts]
-[energy surging]
Hello there, Visitor!
Thank you for saving us!
Wait.
So, you’re okay?
The Star Children are always
automatically protected
by holy Matryoshka dolls
when they’re in
any kind of danger.
Yep! So, you don’t
have to worry about us!
That’s incredible.
But what about your wounds?
Are you saying that
you’re fully recovered?
Right!
We’re both as good as new!
I’m glad to hear it!
You stand no chance
against them right now!
Back to the foster home
for more training!
[VIRGO, CANCER]
Got it!
Itsuki, you must defeat
the Impurities next time.
Yeah, I know.
Apart from everything else,
I can’t stand seeing the Star
Children suffer like that.
So, let’s try again!
Yes, honored Visitor!
Itsuki is beginning to develop
a rather moving sense
of duty as a Visitor.
[giggles]
All that’s left is to improve
his technique
for the all-important
Love Ritual!
After all, he was a total newbie
at sexytime stuff
’til just a few days ago.
So he could use a little help
with his [barking]
in their [meowing] and I’m
just the one to do it,
if I don’t say so myself.
[VIRGO, CANCER]
Help us, Visitor!
They’re way too strong!
Wow, already?
That's rough.
This isn’t good.
We can’t even get close to them.
We gotta have more training.
Don’t you get it?
This is weird!
Something’s really wrong,
Narcisstes!
[NARCISSTES]
Okay, calm down, Mana.
A typical Visitor
would’ve defeated
an Impurity Lord by now!
But he still can’t even seem
to beat a single minion!
[ITSUKI]
I’m sorry.
I know it has to be
my fault, somehow.
Hey, are you even listening?
I think you’ve forgotten, Mana.
The maidens of the twelve
constellations
have never all changed at once
in our entire history.
So, what’re you trying
to say is--
I’m saying that we’re in a real
state of emergency.
So, that’s it?
There’s no possible way
for me to defeat the Impurities?
That’s not what I said.
Our academics know what to do
thanks to ancient texts.
Though such writings
are often disregarded
as being stories
and legends.
Don’t tell me.
Do you mean... ?
Itsuki, listen well, now.
If we’re to get through
this crisis,
you have no choice but to
perform a Double Love Ritual.
[ITSUKI] Um, what's a
Double Love Ritual?
[giggling]
I bet you already know!
It’s a ritual where you have
two sexual partners at once!
Sounds fun, right?
You obviously need
a lot of stamina
for this particular ceremony,
but if you can swing it,
it’s a practical buffet
for the senses!
A feast for your whole body!
Two arms and legs
may not feel like enough,
but remember,
you can always activate
Little Itsuki in the middle,
you pervert, you!
I don’t think I understand.
Fool!
It’s a three[bleep]!
A three[bleep]!
Would you grow a pair
and stop playing dumb?
I’ll put it as simply
as I possibly can:
it’s a lovey-dovey activity
performed by a group
of men and women.
Come on, you know you
wanna try it, right?
I can probably handle
a group activity, yeah.
You’re such a
good little pervert.
By the way, you can use these.
Believe me, this’ll be heaven.
Group cooperative play
that’s two times better
than sixty-nining.
A brand new thing!
That’s a little intimidating.
Don’t worry about a thing!
The Visitor can relax
and leave everything
to the maidens!
You know, it’s, what do you
call it? In Sola.
Oh, you know, the fish
that’s popular for sushi!
Are you talking
about tuna, my fave?
[MANA]
Yes! That! Tuna!
All you need to do
is be present and relax
and focus all of your attention
on one spot.
Just lay there like a dead fish
and the two maidens will happily
tussle and cook you right up!
[NARCISSTES]
According to the ancient texts,
the Star Children
who are born as a product
of the Double Love Ritual
are even more remarkable.
Supposedly, even stronger than
the ones you’ve already made.
Why, "supposedly?"
[NARCISSTES] For at least
the past few hundred years,
a Visitor capable of bonding
with multiple maidens at once
was not thought
to actually exist.
In other words, the Double Love
Ritual is uncharted territory,
even for us.
[ITSUKI]
No pressure, then.
On top of that, we really have
no way of knowing
what kind of damage
this could do to your body.
A Visitor’s bond with a maiden
is very intense.
Well, is there any other way?
[NARCISSTES] I’m sorry.
We can't find a better path
to defeating
the Impurities right now.
Just think about it:
the lucky Visitor with the duty
to bond intimately
with the beautiful maidens
of the twelve
constellations is you!
Isn’t that amazing?
Don’t you feel like
the luckiest?
You should be proud,
you’ll be a pioneer
exploring bold new frontiers!
Just give me
a minute to process.
[MAHIRU]
I wish Mana knew how not subtle
this outing actually is.
We have hot springs
in Granvania,
just like you do in Sola!
It’ll be a great chance
for you both to relax
and get some much
needed R and R.
Not to mention, doing it under
the big, open sky
is liberating as heck!
The only real drawback is,
you might totally
wear yourselves out
and be even more exhausted
when you get back!
[laughs]
Yeah, it’s pretty obvious
he’s up to something again.
What do you mean, "again?"
Well, there’s
this Double Love Ritual
he wants me to do-- Oh!
Oh, don’t stop now.
A Double Love Ritual, huh?
Yeah. Never mind.
Itsuki, you really are one
of the most frustrating people--
-[shouts]
-[ITSUKI grunts]
Don’t worry,
I’ll grab your bag.
What is this?
He’s not lookin’
very good, is he?
Hey! That’s private!
Wait, is that thing
what I think it is?
Don’t get any stupid ideas!
I’m just keeping it
because it’s cute.
It has nothing to do with
the fact that you gave it to me
so get that out of your head!
Wow! I’ve never been to a hot
spring quite like this before!
[ITSUKI] It looks like
there’s only one spring.
[MAHIRU] Who cares?
We’ll go in together.
We used to take baths
together all the time.
Yeah, same same.
Are you kidding me right now?
We were, like,
five years old then!
Stop freaking out.
I’m getting in, so deal with it.
Mahiru, come on!
Cut it out!
Would you please get your dirty
mind out of the gutter?
I came totally prepared
for something like this.
It’s so good.
Feels like I’m about to melt.
Itsuki, aren’t you gonna get in?
Why are you making
such a huge deal about this?
Just take ’em off, already!
Just don’t look, okay?
'Course not.
I’m not the perv around here.
[ITSUKI] Wow.
This place really is wonderful.
Although, it does
sting a little bit.
What’s wrong?
[MAHIRU]
That mark.
[ITSUKI]
Oh, sorry.
Is there dirt on me
or something?
No, it’s not that.
Why do you have
so many injuries?
[ITSUKI]
I guess from training.
It feels like I’ve leveled up
kind of a lot.
Still not strong enough to beat
Impurities, though.
So, you’ll make more, then.
Star Children.
Yes, of course.
I have to try.
What’s wrong, Mahiru?
Hey.
You in there?
Listen well, warrior.
The battles may
be getting tough,
but you are not to die,
understand?
All of a sudden,
you’re concerned?
Shut up and listen to me!
I’m just saying
that you mustn’t die!
I get it. I’ll do my best
not to die
’til I can get you back home.
So is that a promise?
Come on, don’t worry.
The Star Children and I
are always getting stronger.
Next time, we’ll
beat the Impurities.
Despite how she may look,
Mahiru is really a huge crybaby,
so you should probably
keep protecting her.
Don’t worry,
I definitely plan to,
but Mahiru
isn’t really a crybaby, is she?
Yeah, it’s weird.
It’s not like me
to be insecure, is it?
But suddenly, here we are
in this strange place
and they’re telling us
we’ve been chosen
as Visitor and maiden.
And I really can’t believe
that just a few days ago
we were in a love ritual.
-[whimpering]
-[splashing]
[ITSUKI]
Hey, where’d you go?
Oh, my gosh.
What happened to me?
Passed out from the heat.
You okay?
How ya feeling?
[MAHIRU] Wow.
I’m sorry I’ve been such a pain.
[ITSUIKI]
You haven't.
It’s getting kind of
chilly, though.
We should head back.
[MAHIRU]
Okay, let’s go.
Wait, where’s my key chain?
Oh, sorry. I think I was just
so focused on trying
to save you
that I forgot about it.
I’m sure it’s down in the bottom
of the hot spring.
Oh, my gosh, it can’t
be gone. It can't.
Hey, what are you doing?
-[splashing]
-[MAHIRU] It’s freezing!
[ITSUKI] I heard this hot spring
turns into cold water
after sunset.
Why don’t you go get changed?
I’ll wait for you.
You’re the Visitor and the fate
of this world
literally rests in your hands.
I can’t let you catch
a cold or anything!
Don’t worry.
Wait here, okay?
’Kay.
Itsuki.
[ITSUKI]
Found it! Mahiru, I found it!
My sweet little key chain!
[ITSUKI]
Here. Try not to lose it.
I’m so relieved.
Thank you.
Hey, Mahiru.
Once we’ve grown up,
let’s stay together,
just like this, okay?
Itsuki.
No way, you actually remembered!
I did. Just now.
It was always my duty
to be at your side
when you needed help,
wasn’t it?
Sorry I forgot.
But you...
You remembered everything.
You haven’t forgotten
our promise this whole time.
It was silly.
It was just a promise
made between two kids.
I’m being stupid.
Ignore me. 'Kay?
Or don’t.
I don't know.
No way. That’s
the old Mahiru that I...
Sorry to interrupt, but please
hop inside this lovely carriage
and then pick up
where you left off.
You can enjoy deepening your
bond all the way to the shrine.
But don’t forget:
you have to hold it!
No premature anything!
So, keep that in mind
as you play!
You have to hold your bonds
at their peak,
and maintain that all the way
through the Love Ritual, okay?
What? But I...
[giggles] Don’t you worry about
a thing. In exchange,
I packed plenty
of recommended adult toys
for you to use
on your [squeaking]
and on her [squeaking]
and all I can say is, I think
you're gonna thank me, mister!
Ugh, why do you
have to talk about it?
I know where you’re coming from.
Girls in Sola are all waiting
for a prince
on a white horse, right?
If the prince wants some action,
then that’s fine
and dandy, isn’t it?
Oh, wait, I think I see
what’s happening!
Was the mere thought of
alone-sexy-time with
Itsuki enough to get
your [bleep] all [bleep]
and hot and bothered, Mahiru?
[giggles]
Well, if not, don’t worry.
I've got plenty
of lubricating
options in there, including
[bird chirping]-flavored,
so please, help yourself!
Would you just
say something, already?
This one’s not about to complain
about anything.
Getting in this
see-through carriage
is the dream
of every person in Sola.
Apparently, you’re all
kinky freaks
who get off on being watched
by strangers!
Anyway, long story short,
this carriage
makes the dreams
of both men and women come true!
Its name is:
The Granvania Dream Coach!
-This is seriously wrong, Mana.
-Itsuki?
Listen, guys.
This carriage would be very cool
if we could see out
while we’re together,
and nobody could see in,
but that’s not the case!
You can see everything!
It completely ruins all the
excitement and titillation!
[MAHIRU]
Okay. I'm leaving.
All I’m asking is that
you do something
to take care of his wounds!
Got it? I'm counting on you!
But I put so much work
into that particular plan!
It was a masterpiece that took
me ten years to complete!
[ITSUKI] Sorry, but the concept
was lacking.
[MANA] Shut up,
you ungrateful letch!
[REONE] You’ve become noticeably
stronger in such a short time.
[sneezes]
Oh, no. I’m afraid it isn’t
even flu season yet.
-What’s going on?
-Actually...
Long story short,
my perfect and fabulous
Double Love Ritual Plan
was completely ruined!
The legendary Double Love?
Did you really attempt it?
Heh, you bet I did!
I’m not so sure Itsuki should
attempt the Double Love Ritual
in his current condition.
As his doctor, I really
don’t recommend it.
What?
It’ll be okay, though.
I just need to know
what’ll happen to Itsuki’s body.
With that data, we’ll be fine.
I’ll need that info
before the real thing.
My, the real thing.
What an old fashioned way
to refer to it, Reone!
So, you wanna know
what’ll happen to
Itsuki’s Big Magnum
during the ritual?
Come on, we already know
what happens!
But let’s recap.
Are you interested
in the rate of expansion?
Or how long he’ll last?
Or wait!
Do you wanna know his sustained
frictional temperature?
Is that what you need to know?
Mana, let’s go ahead
and have a brief nap.
Now, since I need to collect
your physical data anyway,
I think perhaps
we should practice together.
So, you’ll be...
Yes. If it’s alright with you,
I’ll be one of the two maidens.
And you can decide who will be
the second one.
But...
It must be nice to be young.
I have some apples
if you’d like one.
How about it?
I'll peel it for you.
Or should I just...
rub it a bit
and feed it to you
one bite at a time?
Um, that would be amazing.
You think you could bake it?
What did you just say?
Oh, was that a weird request?
Sorry, not sure
what I was thinking.
No, not at all,
it’s just that you sounded
like my little brother.
Is that him, there?
The one in the photo?
[REONE]
Yes. That was so strange.
It was like having him back
for a second,
hearing the way you said that.
Having him back from where?
Where is your brother at?
He passed away five years ago
after an illness.
Actually, he was about
your age at the time.
I never knew you had such
tragedy in your life, Reone!
Why in the heck didn’t
you ever tell me that?
[REONE] Your treatment concludes
when you finish the apple.
[ITSUKI]
Thanks.
I don’t need any gratitude,
but please bring me another
maiden as soon as possible.
[ITSUKI] How should I decide
on the second maiden?
Mahiru is angry with me,
and I haven’t seen Ruka
since the last time.
[FALUN]
Hey, now. Aren’t we drinking
a tad too slowly over here?
You guys, enjoy!
Let me know if you
need anything, okay?
[MALE BAR PATRON 1]
Sweet Falun,
you’re just as beautiful
as ever!
Hi. So sorry about the wait!
This table ordered
extra beer snacks, right?
[MALE BAR PATRON 2]
Give us a dance, Falun!
You know it puts us
in a drinking mood!
Darn, I guess you
leave me no choice.
Attention!
Who wants to see the world
famous phenomenon,
the Falun dance?
[MALE BAR PATRONS]
We do!
[FALUN]
Okay, okay! You win, as usual!
Someone! Get back there
and start the music.
♪
[MALE BAR PATRON 1]
Aw, come on, don’t stop!
Show us more!
[FALUN]
The night is still young.
Let’s leave some fun
for later, shall we?
Your name’s Falun, right?
You were just incredible
out there.
Well, I am
a professional dancer,
so it’d be weird
if I couldn’t move.
Sorry, do I know you
from somewhere?
Huh? Do you not remember me?
Oh, right, now I’ve got it!
You’re my Visitor!
Sorry about that!
I’m just kidding, of course.
Let me buy you a drink!
I think I’m still too young
to drink legally,
but thanks, though.
You sweet little baby, you.
Does the little man
want some juice?
[ITSUKI]
Um, Falun.
I’d like to ask you about
the Love Ritual.
[FALUN]
Oh. That.
Is it really my turn already?
Welp, let’s get on with it
so you can
save the world, I guess.
[ITSUKI] What’s with the sudden
attitude? Are you angry at me?
[FALUN] Look, I’m a freelance,
traveling dancer
with nowhere to go
and no place to call home.
And out of the blue,
they tell me I'm a maiden
and everything that means.
So, now I’m tied down
to this place.
I never asked for it,
and I can’t stand it.
Sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
I don't know.
Because I’m too weak to fight.
You’re taking
care of that, though.
And thank goodness, because
I feel like I can’t breathe
when I stay
in one place too long.
So, just be aware, I’m gonna
die of suffocation soon.
[gasps]
How’s that?
Better?
I think you’re breathing
just fine now, wouldn’t you say?
Falun. I’ll show you a world
you’ve never seen before,
and I’ll make you feel
things you’ve never felt.
Gah! This book is incredible!
Boom! Atta boy, Itsuki!
You did it! Page fifteen:
Technique for shutting up
needy girls, part three!
Well done, you!
A good start!
You’ve even earned ten
Visitor Perv Points!
You can start, Itsuki.
Yeah, I’m more than ready
to begin.
Are you okay, Itsuki?
Is this a bit too
stimulating for you?
You don’t have to worry
about a single thing.
Leave everything to
your new friend, Falun, okay?
[REONE] Yes. This is only
practice, after all.
No need to feel nervous.
Just be yourself.
Crap. I’m so sorry. I...
Hey, don’t let it get to you!
It happens all the time
when young men are presented
with sexy adult ladies.
I’d say it’s a natural reaction
for healthy male students!
However, I do wish you'd
lasted at least long enough
to experience
a really good lick.
Don't worry. I’m sure you’ll
have plenty more opportunities.
But I’m imagining
how Reone and Falun
must’ve looked
after hearing you moan.
Their imaginations must be
going wild right now,
their whole bodies
thrumming and alive!
-Now’s your chance!
-Do you think so?
Yes, this is no time
to be depressed!
You’re right, okay.
I’ll just get in there
and do my best.
So, ladies, would you
please consider
giving birth to my child?
I’m in your care.
[MANA]
The Love Ritual.
A holy ceremony for giving birth
to Star Children.
For the first time
in hundreds of years,
a Visitor is going to bond with
two maidens at the same time.
The legendary Double Love Ritual
will be performed.
[ITSUKI]
Both of you, together.
[energy surging]
[popping]
Well, hello there!
My name is Capri.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Scorpi.
This is wonderful!
I never knew the Double
Love Ritual
could be quite this majestic.
We really did make
two at one time.
It’s so nice to meet you!
Yes, thank you, Visitor.
I have greatly underestimated
Itsuki’s ability
as an effective
Visitor this entire time.
Looks like Itsuki’s wounds
weren't nearly as severe
as we feared.
Wouldn’t you agree?
[ITSUKI]
Mana, have a look at this!
Congratulations to all!
It was supposed to be practice,
but look, it turned out
to be the real thing!
And look at these perfect
Star Children.
I’ve never seen such
strong kiddos in my life. Wow!
My legs. I don’t think I can
stand up yet.
It feels like I [bleep]
to the ends of the universe.
Itsuki, you wild beast of a boy!
This is it, Itsuki.
I have complete faith in you.
I'm ready. I feel like my body’s
full of good energy!
It’s so awesome, and it's
totally different than before.
It changes things when you have
a whole party with you.
Details on the site!
[ITSUKI] Okay.
Everyone, come on. Follow me!
Right!
We’re with you, Visitor!
All right, let’s go!
[ALL shouting]
And so, Itsuki and his party
defeated the Impurities
and faced an Impurity Lord.
[ITSUKI] This one’s
pretty strong. Be careful, okay?
And try to conserve HP!
Yes, sir, Visitor!
[whimpering]
Don't be scared.
If you sense any danger,
I want you to hide behind me.
Do you understand? Scorpi?
All right.
Let’s go!
And so, Itsuki and his party
emerged victorious
after a super intense battle
with the Impurity Lord.
Woo-hoo!
Well done, Itsuki!
Now, we can offer up
the Star Ward!
Here, all you have to do
is hand it to that altar!
[energy shimmering]
[MANA]
There. The number of Impurities
in the labyrinth
should go down now.
Come on. Let’s go back outside.
Is everyone okay?
Yes.
[ALL]
Okay, this is terrifying!
What was that scream?
It must be...
♪
[MANA]
La, la, la, la, la, la...
La, la!
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
Manasir.