[thunder rumbling]
[MAHIRU]
Ritual of the Great Star Ward?
[SHANGRI-LA]
Yes. The Star Ward offered
to the Thirteenth Phantom,
the last remaining Impurity,
is called the Great Star Ward.
What sets it apart
is that this ward
will be the Visitor himself.
Whoa, hold on!
What's gonna happen to Itsuki
after that?
Itsuki will need
to be sealed inside,
with the Thirteenth Phantom,
for all eternity.
Wait, what?
And you want us
to perform the ritual?
Are you serious?
Granvania will be doomed
unless you do.
[ALL gasp]
[NARCISSTES] Itsuki has accepted
the burden of becoming
the Great Star Ward.
This is what he wants to do.
That can't be.
Itsuki...
About being
the Great Star Ward...
I think I'll have to pass.
Oh, why the sudden
change of heart?
I'm sure it's because now
he has something truly special
to keep living for,
isn't that right, sweetie pie?
-Sweetie pie?
-Huh?
Those two sure are
getting along strangely well.
Did something happen
between them?
Oh, I think
they've done it, for sure.
Probably why she's acting
like a new girlfriend.
It's just... I want to keep
fighting until the end.
Well, you have
my full support.
[ITSUKI]
Thank you, Alfie.
You'll have me
right beside you,
so, what could
possibly go wrong?
[thunder rumbling]
[MANA]
I'm pretty impressed that you
decided to fight the phantom.
[ITSUKI]
If I sacrificed myself,
Granvania would be saved.
That would be
the safe choice, but...
[ITSUKI]
I'm not finished living yet.
You sure aren't! We have
a beautiful life, a happy home,
and a brilliant future
waiting for us, Itsuki!
Huh?
Uh, right.
Anyway, I have to fight
for my future,
but you didn't have
to join me, Mana.
[MANA]
You go, I go, silly!
How else could I feel
after experiencing
such a passionate embrace?
When that happened, the little
ladybug in me came out
and started dancing the samba
for all she was worth!
Ladybug?
You've become part of
who I am, now, baby.
Which means I'll follow you
forever,
to the ends of the universe!
How sweet.
Thank you, Mana.
Ooh.
Wow, those words just shot
straight to my uterus.
I'm totally yours now, Itsuki.
If there was every any doubt.
Totally yours.
Heart, mind, body, and soul,
forever and ever, amen!
I can sense its power
from here.
[MANA] Oh, me, too!
I can feel it pulsing through me
like crazy right now!
[exploding]
[MANA yelling]
[roaring]
The Thirteenth Phantom,
I presume.
Get ready to be brought down.
I'm gonna live!
What?
[groaning]
[MANA]
Darling!
-[thudding]
-[crumbling]
-I'm all right.
-Thank goodness!
[roaring]
Do you think
the Visitor is gonna be okay?
I don't know, maybe
we should've gone with him.
-I bet it's not too late!
-Let's go!
No way.
Itsuki gave us instructions.
[ITSUKI] You'll have to
protect everyone here, okay?
Alfie, will you please
take care of the kids?
Yes, of course I will!
So, it's obvious that I'm the
woman he cares for the most.
He's asking me to safeguard
the proof of our love.
Done!
I don't really think
that's what he said.
No, also, she's not my mom.
My mom is Leone.
Yeah, and I'm Femiruna's kid.
Mahiru is my mom.
Okay, you're missing
the point, here.
He's trusting me with his
most precious things.
Oh, gosh! This must be exactly
what housewives feel like
when their husbands
go off to work!
Wait, don't housewives cheat
on their husbands, as a rule?
I thought all they
did was seduce
their husbands' bosses
and neighbors and stuff.
So, if Alfie's a housewife
that means she's a temptress.
Housewives do not always
cheat on their husbands!
Who the heck taught you
something so ridiculous?
The raccoon
who acts like his lover!
[chuckles]
We'll have words
when she gets back.
[SHANGRI-LA]
There's not much time left.
Right. We need to begin
the Ritual of the Great
Star Ward, now.
We can't.
If you don't, this world
will be overrun with Impurities.
And if that happens,
then you won't ever
be able to return
to your home in Sola again!
[REONE]
Mahiru.
[MAHIRU] We, the powers
who transcend time and space,
hereby terminate
the path of chaos.
Damn it! My attacks aren't even
scratching this thing!
Let's just run.
We'll go far away
and live quietly together
on a little cul-de-sac!
You know I can't
run away from this.
I have no choice but to stop it.
What the...?
[MANA] The Ritual of
the Great Star Ward?
[ITSUKI yelling]
And now, be filled
with the light.
Eliminate the darkness
completely.
[MANA]
Oh, Itsuki! Please, no!
[MAHIRU] I command the law
of the universe.
Turn this soul into
the Great Star Ward
and place the chaos
into eternal sleep.
Now and forever.
[SHANGRI-LA]
What is it?
Continue the ritual!
I can't do this!
I can't sacrifice Itsuki!
[grunting]
-You're alive!
-What happened?
[MANA] The ritual was
stopped somehow!
My love!
[rocks tumbling, crashing]
You couldn't do it,
after all?
I'm sorry, sir.
But I just won't sacrifice
Itsuki.
I know there has to be
some other way.
Even if the world is saved,
it's pointless if he's gone.
I know that now.
Well?
Is there another way?
[NARCISSTES]
There may be.
Mirei.
I was going through
old documents in the castle,
and I discovered one ancient
sheaf in the library which said:
"If the Visitor is able to truly
bond with each of the maidens,
they have the power to kill
the Impurities, for good."
[NARCISSTES] There wasn't
any more detail in the document,
so we don't know exactly
how it's accomplished.
It's likely a hopeless dream.
[MAHIRU] But there could
be a way to avoid
sacrificing Itsuki
if we at least try, right?
It's too much of a gamble.
Maybe so,
but we have to try.
I ask you, now.
Do what you can to help Itsuki!
You can change the fate
of this world!
He said yes.
Thank you!
I know that we can do it!
Let's go, you guys!
Are you sure about this?
I didn't feel right
about sacrificing him.
He doesn't deserve that.
What is this?
Everyone, get ready!
That's a really
powerful Impurity.
It's close.
[energy surging]
[ALFIE]
It's the Thirteenth Phantom.
That thing came out of there
alone, which means Itsuki...
It's our turn to fight back.
Remember, we have our
instructions from the Visitor.
It's our duty to protect
this world from them.
I don't know if I...
[VIRGO]
You stay here and protect Alfie.
Don't worry, we'll go
take care of that thing.
[MAHIRU]
He's right.
[ALFIE]
You guys.
We're here because
we'd like to help, too.
We cherish Granvania
as much as anyone.
We can't just stand by.
And we refuse
to sacrifice Itsuki.
So, we're here to support him
however we can!
[energy surging]
It's like the maidens'
and Star Children's powers
have synchronized!
[STAR CHILDREN yelling]
Mana!
You just saved my life!
Hey, no worries.
It was a piece of cake.
[ITSUKI] So, the Ritual of
the Great Star Ward failed?
The maidens must have
decided to stop it.
[ITSUKI]
Mahiru and the others?
But then, what are we gonna do
about the Thirteenth Phantom?
[MANA] Well, there's only
one thing you can do.
You have to defeat it.
I won't remind you of the
burden to save all of Granvania.
Just think of it as
fighting to protect
-the ones you care about.
-Mana.
This is the very last thing
I can give you, Itsuki.
The last thing?
No, please don't say that!
Oopsie!
Where did that come from?
Okay, truth be told,
this is what I was saving
to invigorate you
for our first night together!
Don't tell, but I kinda
"borrowed" it from Shangri-La.
It's so you can save the world!
I've always known
I could count on you, Mana.
I support my man!
[ITSUKI]
All right, let's go!
[energy surging]
[STAR CHILD 1] Shoot,
this isn't working at all!
[STAR CHILD 2]
What's with this guy?
[STAR CHILD 3]
No fair!
[ALL gasping]
[attack yelling]
-Itsuki!
-You're still alive!
You all right?
[MAHIRU]
That's supposed to be our line!
You made the decision
to sacrifice yourself alone?
What the hell were you thinking?
-Yes, yes!
I'm really sorry.
Now, I know.
I don't want to become
the Great Star Ward.
I wanna be here,
with each one of you!
Translation:
he wants to bang all of us!
Oh, well...
You've been through a lot,
so we'll forgive you.
Right, girls?
[ALL whimpering]
Well, we'll just have to beat
the Thirteenth Phantom,
won't we?
Everyone!
I'll need all your strength!
[attack yelling]
[STAR CHILD 1]
I won't let you hurt them!
[STAR CHILD 2]
Me, neither!
[STAR CHILD 3]
We will protect the maidens!
Watch out!
I'm so glad...
I was able to protect you.
[ITSUKI yelling]
[ITSUKI]
You're okay! You have to be!
Don't you see?
I was able to keep you safe.
Which means that I've finally
fulfilled my sacred duty
as a Star Child!
You deserve to live!
We'll just have to heal
that wound!
Mana!
I need more of the potion.
I'm sorry,
but it won't help her.
What are you talking about?
Stop it!
Give me the potion!
Itsuki, it's too late.
I don't want you to worry
about me, okay?
Remember, this is what I was
meant to do, from the beginning.
I was born as a Star Child,
then became a maiden.
And later,
I was able to love
and protect you, Itsuki.
That makes me so happy.
You deserve a lot more
than this kind of "happiness."
Much more.
It's not fair.
We were just starting out!
Yeah, I know we were.
Hey, would you like to make me
happier, right now?
Somehow I knew
you'd be able to do it.
Itsuki,
I'm happier
than I've ever been.
Alfie.
Don't you see?
Because of you,
I got to experience
what it's like being in love.
Thank you.
Really.
[shimmering]
-This can't be.
-Please, no!
Alfie!
You're gonna pay
for this, Phantom.
I'll never forgive you!
[MIREI]
The emblem of the Ophiuchus.
Oh, Alfie.
You still thought only of
Itsuki right up to the very end!
She was right. That's what we
should all be doing!
Absolutely.
We're all with you, Mahiru.
We'll fight this together.
I won't give up
till this is done.
Let's just hurry up
and beat that thing!
Otherwise, it's gonna
destroy our whole world.
I'll do anything to prevent
that from happening!
Come on!
Let's kick its ass!
If we beat it,
the animals will be safe.
So let's do it.
I'm not even close
to being finished
with my adventures, yet!
I want to bake more bread!
There are so many
more things I wanna draw!
One thing is certain,
we each love this world!
We're sending you
all of our strength!
And our love!
Combine!
The Visitor, the maidens,
and the Star Children,
have all joined together
to become one!
Their combined power is
what will defeat the Impurity!
Itsuki!
We're all behind you!
[ITSUKI]
Combined Mecha Beam!
Oh, wow! That's the true form
of the Thirteenth Phantom!
I don't like the look
of that thing one bit.
Visitor, why do you reject me?
The phantom actually speaks?
Answer me.
Why do you reject me?
[ITSUKI]
Because you're an Impurity!
[THIRTEENTH PHANTOM]
That's right. I am an Impurity.
The destroyer of everything
in this world.
However, you should remember,
you humans created me.
[ITSUKI]
Shut up!
[THIRTEENTH PHANTOM] I am
the manifestation of your filth.
The result of humans defiling
each other with your own hands.
The offspring of your lust.
Your Impurity!
[ITSUKI yelling]
Itsuki!
Visitor.
I want to see you struggle.
-[energy crackling]
-[ITSUKI yelling]
That's more like it.
Surely, you must have enjoyed
and taken comfort
in all of those dark exchanges.
I'm sure it was well worth
this current pain
to defile your maidens!
Come, accept me.
Become one with me,
and together,
we'll defile every corner
of this world!
Hurry!
You must accept me to survive!
Like hell, I will!
You make it seem as though
loving is defiling!
In a way, it's true.
Love is messy.
But that's not all it is!
I came to care about them!
And because of all of that love,
the Star Children were born!
If the love of human beings
brings impurities
into the world,
then the Star Children are born
as a hope to get rid of them!
That's what Alfie, and every
other person here has taught me!
Oh, Itsuki.
Alfie.
[yelling]
[ITSUKI]
Rasaru!
[energy bursting, shimmering]
Well done, Visitor!
You can leave the rest to us.
This is our duty
and we're happy to do it!
[defeated groaning]
Thank you so much
for making me.
[ALL]
We love you, Visitor!
Thank you for giving birth
to us!
Bye-bye!
You guys.
[giggling]
♪
[MAHIRU]
Trouble deciding what to do?
-Yeah.
-Well...
I'm not surprised.
I'm gonna go back, though.
I'm so ready to see
my mom and dad again.
The other world
is where I belong.
It is sad to leave everyone.
But you should follow
your heart, Itsuki.
You have things to stay for.
I get that.
Wait, Mahiru.
I'm going back, too.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I've done my duty.
It's time.
[footsteps approaching]
Hey, guys.
Sorry. But we've decided
to return home.
[MAHIRU]
Looks like you found out.
If this is what the two
of you have decided.
Well, then, of course we'll see
you off with a big smile.
Yes. It's sad, but we
understand missing home.
I'll admit, I was hoping
to get more research
done about Visitors.
Goodbye.
Please, take care
of yourselves, okay?
Know what? Maybe I'll even
see you again on my travels!
Um, that doesn't seem
very likely, though.
Oh, well. I guess that's
just the way it goes.
Bye, my friends.
I had so much fun with you.
You guys, this is from us.
We got together
and wrote you a letter.
I drew you a picture.
Please, take it.
And here's some bread I made.
I hope you like it!
Guys. I'm not good at "sad."
Not at all.
I simply cannot!
Think of happy thoughts!
Thank you all!
We're never gonna forget.
Goodbye!
No, I'm not ready
to say goodbye.
I don't want to, yet!
-Same, here!
-Wait for me!
I don't want
a goodbye, either.
-Wait!
-Where is everyone going?
[COLLETTE]
Let's open a bakery together!
[LILITH]
Or, be a comedy trio!
[FEMIRUNA]
Take me with you!
That's cheating, you guys!
I just want to
study you a bit more!
I wanted you to be a model
for my paintings!
[gasping]
[ALL yelling]
[ALFIE]
Well, me, too, then!
[MANA]
And me!
[ALL yelling]
[splashing]
Was that...?
Ow.
That hurt.
Wait, You followed us?
The gate has closed.
No going back, now.
Don't worry, it's all
gonna work out fine.
Oh yeah, for sure it will!
[ITSUKI]
Wha-- Alfie?
Oh my gosh, and all
the Star Children, too?
How?
[ALFIE]
Who knows?
Looks like we were revived,
somehow!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[ITSUKI]
Wait, who the hell is that?
Mana, duh.
[ALL]
What?
What can I say?
I guess
I was showered with
so much of your love
that the woman inside me
was awakened!
You perv! You laid hands
on a raccoon, too?
What the heck do you
mean, "too"?
I've never "laid hands"
on anyone!
I'm a gentleman!
Except, don't forget.
You definitely gave me
a big kiss!
[ALL gasping]
Oh, right, I did.
But, more to the point.
What are we gonna do now,
Mahiru?
Well, there's only one option.
We'll care for them.
Wanna come over?
[ALL]
Let's go!
[bell tolling]
Everyone.
Will you give
birth to my child?
[MAIDENS]
We will!