♪
Welcome, viewers!
We're thrilled to say
that everyone's favorite
reality dating show
has finally made its way
to Granvania.
The lucky fellow we've chosen
to be our bachelor
is Itsuki Yuge.
Some of you might
know him better
as our latest Visitor
from Sola!
Just look at that handsome mug.
We've gathered
12 bombshell contestants.
The question is: who will be
the one to win Itsuki's heart?
These maidens have come
from every part of our world,
representing a wide range
of ages and backgrounds.
The one thing
they all have in common
is that each one is determined
to find love with our bachelor.
So, stick around and watch
these 12 beauties
try to win
over Bachelor Itsuki!
You'll be on the edge your seat
as they compete
in intense romantic challenges
to be the lucky winner
of the Ultimate Love Ritual!
Get ready for devious plots,
petty jealousies,
shaky alliances,
shocking betrayals,
and other wild shenanigans!
The girls selected to stick
around will be chosen in:
The Sushi Ceremony!
What is the Ultimate
Love Ritual, you ask?
Stay tuned and find out!
[MANA]
Good evening, ladies.
I'm the Visitor's servant, Mana.
As you know, the duty of maidens
is to give birth
to Star Children.
However, surprising
though it is,
some of you still have yet
to fulfill that duty.
Mirei, Sue.
I'm looking at you right now.
Therefore, I have prepared
the Ultimate Love Ritual
as a little extra incentive!
[MIREI]
"Ultimate" how?
What does that mean?
What's the Ultimate Love Ritual?
Tsk, tsk, tsk,
I can't tell you that!
You'll find out once you
experience it for yourself!
It's truly a sacred
sensory paradise
that'll shoot you right off
to the heavens!
However, the sad news is,
only the one maiden
who captures
Visitor Itsuki's heart
will be able
to enjoy it with him!
A passionate date battle
will now ensue
in order to determine
our super lucky winner!
A message from
Visitor Itsuki has arrived.
Please read it out loud,
if you would.
[MAHIRU] "Let's spend time
strengthening our bond
"so we'll 'stick together.'
The person who will join me
for today's date is Sue!"
-[MAIDENS gasping]
-[MANA] What the heck?
She's gone!
[clucking]
Shh, they'll find you.
[MANA] Huh, I distinctly
remember saying
you couldn't
bring animals with you.
I'm really sorry.
But this is Quelquelle.
And...
he gets lonely...
[MANA] Get off! What,
did you sense I was releasing
a lot of pheromones earlier,
so now you're all turned on?
You fowl pervert!
Gross, your comb is all red
and swollen!
No, he's just excited 'cause
he's not used to strangers.
It's all right.
You'll be just fine.
Good boy.
Come on, we need to hurry!
Itsuki is very much looking
forward to your date.
Okay, then.
-Good to see you.
-You, too.
I want to learn everything
I can about you today.
-[tires screeching]
-[window motor whirring]
[ITSUKI]
I hope you don't mind.
I asked the animals to join us
on our date.
Great!
So tell me a little about 'em.
You're the one who cares
for these guys, right?
Yes.
I brought them to the academy.
They came with me from home.
Each and every one of them
has been a dear friend to me.
[ITSUKI]
They're cute.
Yes, they are, aren't they?
They're usually pretty
smelly and loud,
so it's actually kinda rare
for people to have anything nice
to say about them.
So, thanks.
That means a lot.
Of course.
They seem sweet to me.
So I've prepared a feast
for them.
[MANA] How's that for
a fruit basket? Am I right?
Eat up!
Eat!
[splashing]
[MANA]
Oh, gosh, not there! Wait!
[SUE]
Did you know, a long time ago,
they used to study animals
outside the town limits?
That's what my parents did.
They studied animals.
My dad was a researcher
and Mom was a veterinarian.
My favorite thing in the world
was to be hugged by them.
But then, one day, they...
Please don't feel
like you have to tell me.
It's all right.
In this moment, I feel like
I want you to know everything.
That day, Mom and Dad
were attacked by Impurities
that came close to town,
where they were working.
They wrapped me in their arms,
holding and protecting me
until the Impurities went away.
That terrible day
was the last time
either of them
ever embraced me!
But, the truth is...
My heart is still in torment
over what happened.
I can't seem to accept
that my parents are gone.
I can't wrap my head around
never seeing them again!
But afterwards,
I had these animals with me.
They kept me going,
even though I was sad.
I never knew that.
It was great.
She really opened up.
We were able to talk through
a lot of things
and I feel like our bond
was strengthened.
I'll never be able to forgive
the Impurities
that attacked Sue's parents.
Because of my duty
as the Visitor,
but also due to my
growing feelings for Sue.
♪
I'm so bored.
I wonder what kind of date
he took Sue on tonight.
I'm curious.
By the way, Mahiru,
how did your first
Love Ritual go,
and don't leave anything out!
My first love ritual?
I mean, mine was a total
piece of cake, so...
-Really?
-Sure was.
What about you?
Oh, I don't know.
I guess I don't remember.
It was embarrassing.
Geez! Would you stop trying
to get me to talk?
Yes. I understand that Itsuki
is working as hard
as he can to try
and get us back to our world.
Of course he is.
And I know the Love Ritual
is a key part
of making that happen.
I'm lucky 'cause the other girls
are all very sweet.
I wish them nothing
but the best.
[ITSUKI] Thanks, I had
a really fun time today.
Oh, no. I should thank you.
You're welcome!
I'll show you how I feel!
Sushi rice at the bottom.
Plenty of love inside.
And a perfectly shiny fish
on top!
Complete!
[SUE]
Bateira! I love it!
Did you know it means
"small boat" in Portuguese?
[ITSUKI] My heart dips and sways
with love for you, Sue.
Will you accept it?
[gasping]
Thanks so much.
[barking, mooing, clucking]
Well, well.
That was kind of a shock, right?
Who would've guessed the bateira
sushi would be offered to Sue
so soon!
That's quite a turn of events.
Yeah, I agree!
But can you explain
something to me?
What is the sushi thing about?
Wait, are you kidding?
How do you not know that?
Fortunately, I'm prepared, so
just take a good look at this.
The Visitor is allowed
to make bateira sushi
for anyone
he's feeling drawn to.
More to the point, only maidens
who have been given the sushi
can remain in the competition.
[ALFIE]
Oh, now I get it!
Great. Let's catch up with Mana
back on the scene.
Mana?
-Hi, there!
-What are your thoughts?
The sushi, right off the bat!
Not enough prior stimulation
at all, if you ask me.
What do you mean, "stimulation"?
[MANA] Nothing!
The real battle has just begun!
I'll set up a dirty date filled
with all kinds
of nasty perversion
for you sickos to enjoy
in front of your TV!
Oh, you love it, don't you?
Don't you?
-Admit it!
-[continuous tone]
[MANA] I have some
wonderful news, ladies!
You've received a second
invitation from Itsuki.
This time, there's going to be
a group date!
The participants are:
Lily.
Arie.
Falun.
Femiruna.
Leone.
Mirei.
The Visitor's
a very mysterious
being from an alternate world
called Sola.
I can't think of a more
fascinating subject to research.
So, I will. I plan to discover
everything I can about Itsuki.
Research is the reason I'm here.
The only reason.
[MANA] Welcome, maidens,
one and all! Itsuki is waiting
in the room at the end
of these stairs in front of you!
Only the one who reaches
the top first
can advance to the private date!
Easy, right? Or is it?
This next part is a present
from me to you.
Enjoy!
[gasping]
[splashing]
[MANA]
Lotion! Isn't it nice?
Moisten the heck outta
that skin, dear ones!
Let it saturate!
Super soft and smooth flesh
for everyone!
[gasping, groaning]
Now, climb!
What's wrong, you ninnies?
You can't stop now!
Keep going!
Not good.
I can't hang on any longer!
No, wait!
Please don't let go!
Hold onto it!
Don't you dare!
[shrieking]
[yelling]
[screaming]
[thudding]
Okay, Lord, it's time
to give me your strength!
[yelling]
[MANA] Whoa!
The one with the perseverance
to make it to the top is:
Mirei!
[yelling]
Mirei, you made it
over to see me.
Thank you for that.
No. You don't have to thank me.
You know, if you want to,
you can take a bath
and wash all that lotion off.
Yes, that sounds
wonderful, thanks.
I can't see too well
without my glasses.
I think my vision's
gotten a bit worse again.
[ITSUKI]
Here, give me your hand.
How's that?
Is this all right?
Yes, thank you.
[laughs]
Is something funny?
No. I just realized
how nice it is
to occasionally leave myself
in someone else's capable hands.
This rose scent is lovely.
Hey. Mirei.
Are you sure
you're comfortable
being this close?
I am. That okay?
You see, since my eyesight
is so poor,
I'm a little more sensitive to
touch than most people would be.
The sweet heat
coming off your body,
the unique texture of your skin.
Oh, yes, quite intriguing.
This is a feeling
I've never experienced before.
[ITSUKI] Mirei, are you sure
you're comfortable
with everywhere
we're touching?
[MIREI] Absolutely. Let's stay
right here for a while.
What's this? I can't see well,
but it's very hard.
[ITSUKI]
Uh, that's, uh...
Is anything wrong?
[ITSUKI]
Not "wrong" exactly.
I just don't think
you get what you're doing.
Look at that!
What a fascinating reaction.
-Now to collect more data.
-[ITSUKI shrieks]
It's all for research,
you know.
See, since my vision's blurry,
it makes me want
to keep touching
and maybe... lean into you,
and depend on you a lot more
than I typically would.
So... I hope that's okay.
Before today, I've only
ever seen the super cool
and collected side
of her, you know?
When she showed me
this part of herself,
my heart skipped a beat.
You wanna know where
she touched me
under the bubbles, huh?
You know what?
I think I'm gonna leave it
to your imagination.
-[ITSUKI] Mirei.
-Hmm?
[ITSUKI]
Please have some sushi!
[MIREI]
Thank you.
You've decided to keep me.
How brave, Itsuki.
[moaning]
[sighs]
I've decided.
You should stay with me
a lot longer for my research.
And you don't have to worry
because I promise
I won't do anything too scary.
Unless you want me to.
[chuckles]
[MANA]
And so,
Itsuki and the maidens
went on one gorgeous,
memorable date after another.
And the ones who remained
at the end were:
Mirei and Sue!
It's all come down to these
two maidens.
Who do you think he'll choose?
Get cozy and settle in
as we watch
how Itsuki decides to approach
these two very lucky ladies!
[shimmering]
[SUE]
Meow!
Meow.
The truth is, this kitty cat,
she can get pretty lonely
by herself.
So you have to take time
and play with her.
Are you willing to take
good care of her?
Yeah, of course.
I love animals and I've always
secretly wished I had a tail.
I mustered up my courage
and put it on today.
It looks good on you.
You know something?
I get this really steamy
feeling in my heart
whenever I'm around you.
[ITSUKI]
Steamy?
[SUE] I don't know.
Warm and comfortable.
It's a similar feeling as when I
was embraced by my mom and dad.
But I think now I might be
getting a little scared.
Scared of what?
Of me?
It's just that I've lived
alone all this time,
so I'm afraid, if you spoil me,
then I'll become weak.
And then I really might
not survive without you.
[ITSUKI] There's nothing wrong
with needing people.
[SUE]
But...
[ITSUKI]
Sue, you've been on your own,
struggling alone
since your parents left.
I actually think you deserve
to be spoiled a bit.
But what will I do
if you end up leaving me,
just like my mom
and dad did?
It could happen.
You could just
suddenly disappear.
Sue.
I don't want you
to go to the labyrinth!
I don't want you to
put yourself in danger!
I don't want to lose you,
Itsuki!
I'm scared.
Hey, don't worry.
Living in this world
for a little while,
it's made me want to protect
everyone who lives here.
That's honestly how I feel.
To make that happen,
though.
I'll need to create a stronger
Star Child than ever before,
using the Ultimate Love Ritual.
[SUE]
Okay.
I promise you.
I'll defeat the Impurities,
and then I'll come back to you.
[MANA] I sure hope
that wasn't private!
We've heard your entire
conversation!
Learning about Sue's story
has made me do a little deep
thinking and now, I do believe
I've reached a final conclusion!
What conclusion?
Well, Sue and Mirei
have been competing to be
selected by you as the winner.
But honestly, there's no reason
the Ultimate Love Ritual
has to be limited
to one on one!
So, you're suggesting...
[MANA] Yes, an Ultimate
Double Love Ritual!
Assuming that's all right
with Sue.
I want to respect her feelings.
For my part,
I wholeheartedly agree
to doing the ritual
all together.
It means I'll be able to gather
even more interesting data!
Wow, both of us
at the same time?
I think I'd be way
too embarrassed to do that.
There's just no way.
I'm sorry, Mana.
I won't force her.
She isn't comfortable with it.
Not a problem.
I was actually expecting you
to say that.
Now, I want you to trust me.
I'm a researcher, after all.
So, I'm fully prepared
for an event such as this.
I've been wanting to test it.
This medicine should improve
Love Rituals.
Why don't we give it a taste?
What?
Okay, wait.
What is that?
Mirei! Stop!
Stay back!
No!
Just a hypnosis gas
of my own design.
You'll see. Now Sue
won't be embarrassed,
and she'll be more honest
about her feelings, to boot.
You okay, Sue?
Sue?
Meow!
As a little added
bonus for you,
I've also included
a very effective
sensitivity-increasing gas,
you lucky lovers!
It'll benefit the Love Ritual
because it increases
not just
your physical sensations,
but your feelings, too!
Kitty!
Here, kitty, kitty!
Oh here, kitty, kitty!
Come here, wittle kitty!
Kitty!
Oh, kitty, kitty, kitty!
Come here!
This kitty has
a very cute little meow.
[MANA chuckling]
It should definitely start
working on you any second now
if it isn't already, Mirei!
I feel so amazing.
This is just wild!
So intense!
[MANA]
I can't stand it!
I cannot!
This is the best!
Nothing beats watching a pent-up
Type-A lose control
of themselves!
Come on!
What are you waiting for?
The maidens are totally
ready for you!
All that's left to do
is to fulfill your role
as the Visitor!
Yeah!
Will you have my child, please?
-You bet I will!
-Mm... yes!
-[ITSUKI laughing]
-[SUE, MIREI giggling]
Wait!
Hold on, back off, you guys!
Relax! Calm down!
Halt! Desist!
Weirdos, there's no food
on me now!
Don't you get it?
Oh, no. My body
is really sensitive
from that gas.
Hey, stop looking at me
like a bunch of naughty,
naughty beasts.
Oh, it's too dirty,
this is too good,
you nasty,
perverted things, you!
Wait, what are you doing?
Don't stop! Yes!
Right there!
That's right!
It's about to get crazy!
More, more!
Yes!
But back to the ritual.
And so, the bond between Itsuki
and the two maidens
strengthened,
and two strong
Star Children were born!
[ALFIE]
Itsuki, I watched the show!
What a ride!
And I have to say,
I was totally surprised
by the way it all ended.
It's hard not to be embarrassed.
But, hey, two, strong
Star Children were born.
That's what matters, right?
Yeah. The offering of the Star
Wards is going smoothly, too.
At this rate,
it won't be too long
before we can seal
each of the 12 Labyrinths
of Constellations.
[ALFIE]
That's amazing.
I expected nothing less.
But, after you fulfill your duty
as Visitor,
you'll be going back to your
home in Sola, isn't that right?
I guess, soon, I won't be
able to see you anymore.
I mean, not that that matters.
Please don't mind me, okay?
[roaring]
There's that roar again!
Itsuki!
You have to come to the castle!
[SHANGRI-LA] It looks as though
we're all assembled.
Please, feel free to begin.
Well, I've just been researching
the ancient documents,
and I've discovered
that Granvania
apparently has another labyrinth
in addition
to the 12 Labyrinths
of Constellations.
Are you kidding me?
[NARCISSTES] The ancient
document before you
describes the existence
of a thirteenth labyrinth.
According to the writings,
there's a being sealed
inside of it which is referred
to as the "thirteenth phantom."
[ITSUKI]
By "thirteenth phantom,"
does that mean
it's something different
-from the Impurity Lords?
-[MANA] You got that right.
It seems this
"thirteenth phantom"
is actually the source
of the Impurities in this world.
In other words, the Impurities
will just be revived
all over again
unless we seal it, fast.
How can that be?
[NARCISSTES]
We haven't found the entrance
to the thirteenth
labyrinth, though,
or figured out how
we can prevent the revival.
We need to make a request
of you, our Visitor.
Will you offer the help
of the remaining
Star Wards of the constellations
in our search for the answers?
Absolutely.
It would appear the Visitor
now has a brand new duty.
Sealing off the thirteenth
phantom is no small feat.
I'm afraid it'll be an even
tougher challenge
than before, Itsuki.
[ITSUKI]
Yes.
What's on
your mind, Mana?
Well, before now,
there were 12 labyrinths
and 12 maidens.
But since the existence of
the thirteenth labyrinth
has come to light, I have
a feeling that must mean...
Congratulations!
I think we can assume from this
that there's also a thirteenth
maiden out there for you!
So, as soon as you finish
the Love Rituals
with the 12 maidens, you'll
have a new girl to discover!
Oh, no, nose-bleed time!
Yeah, yeah.
Wonder where she is.
Could it be me, by any chance,
I wonder aloud, hopefully?
I can learn to like beasts.
Oh my, you've gone through
quite the transformation.
And anyway, I've got
someone else in mind.
Who says the maiden
has to be a girl?
The answer is, nobody!
Sure, maybe.
Oh, my wow!
So, you're saying,
maybe our next episode
can be a Boys' Love Ritual?
No! But you know what?
I actually wish it was.
Our female viewership
would go through the roof,
that's for sure!
Maybe goodbye, doesn't
really have to be forever.
Pizza Margherita.