[ITSUKI] The relatives I've been
staying with have a daughter.
Her name is Mahiru Konatsuki.
-[lightning]
-[shimmering]
[footsteps]
[door creaks open]
[MAHIRU]
Thanks for coming.
Of course.
What's going on?
[MAHIRU]
It's hard for me to talk about.
[ITSUKI]
Take your time.
Well, as it turns out,
[MAHIRU]
I can't do it.
I can't even bring myself
to tell you.
Hey, come on,
we've been friends forever.
You can tell me anything.
[MAHIRU] I'll try, but I have
to psych myself up first.
Just give me a minute, okay?
[ITSUKI]
Yeah, sure.
[MAHIRU]
The thing is...
I'm, um...
-Well, I'm pregnant.
-[gasps]
It's true.
I'm having a child.
[MAHIRU] I mean, we have been
living together for three years
and you haven't been able
to keep your hands off me.
Not to mention all the times
we've expressed our love
to each other all over the city.
Guess the universe
finally took the hint
and decided
we should be parents.
Uh-- What?
Come on, you know
I'm just teasing.
Our relationship has never
been anything like that.
Listen, is this for real?
-Are you sure?
-Um-hmm.
Although, I hate to admit it,
but I guess this is a case
of truth being stranger
than fiction.
Whoa.
[MAHIRU]
I bet you'd like to know
whose baby it is.
No, I...
I'm just...
I'm more concerned about you
right now, Mahiru.
Thanks for that.
I'm doing okay at the moment.
But, you need to hear the rest.
About who
the father is, so...
[gasps]
[energy surging]
[BOTH gasping]
[yelling]
[ITSUKI grunting]
Mahiru... ?
Mahiru!
[MAHIRU whimpering]
Hey.
Where are we?
These look like
some kind of ruins.
How can you be
so weirdly calm?
Am I?
I guess compared
to my pregnancy,
this isn't the freakiest thing
that's happened this week.
In any case,
we need to work on
finding a way out of here.
It's no place for someone
in your condition.
[MAHIRU]
Listen, Itsuki.
What I was saying before...
About what?
About who the baby's father is.
It's okay.
You don't have to tell me.
[MAHIRU]
Just listen, will you?
The truth is, the person
who got me pregnant...
That person doesn't exist.
What?
[MAHIRU]
I mean, I've never even had...
Look, I don't have to spell it
out for you, do I?
Wait, how the hell
could that possibly be right?
About a week ago
is when I noticed it.
Something about my body
was different.
I started looking online,
and all my symptoms seemed to
point toward me being pregnant.
I took a few different
home pregnancy tests,
and every time,
it was positive.
I was at a loss.
I didn't know what to do.
It didn't make any sense.
[ITSUKI]
Have you seen a doctor?
Not yet.
I'm too scared.
And by the way,
I haven't told anyone else
besides you, either.
Good to know.
Itsuki, thanks for
letting me confide in you.
Just getting it off my chest
like that actually helped
more than I thought.
Good, but you gotta
see a doctor.
I'll go with you.
Thanks, Itsuki.
[groans]
[ITSUKI]
What is it? Mahiru!
[MAHIRU]
I suddenly feel sick.
[ITSUKI]
What? Is it morning sickness?
-[exploding]
-[MAHIRU cries out]
[pained grunt]
[whimpering]
[whimpering continues]
-[pained yelling]
-[energy surging]
[screams]
Mahiru!
[growling]
What the hell?
Crap!
[roaring]
-[snarling]
-[evil chuckling]
[ITSUKI]
Okay.
If I don't do something...
I'm dead!
For sure!
[growling]
[gasps]
-[shimmering]
-[exploding]
Mahiru. Are you okay?
I'm... yeah.
Surprisingly, I'm just fine.
[roaring]
[panting]
[MAHIRU]
Look.
[birds chirping]
[ITSUKI]
Where in the world are we?
[MAHIRU] Maybe we're inside
someone's bad dream.
Huh?
What's that mark
on your hand?
You have one, too.
Right there on your cheek.
[MAHIRU]
I do!
And it's the same as yours!
Well, we may be
terrified and confused,
but at least we're twins!
Dude, so gross.
Who wants to look like you?
[BOTH laughing]
You still feel okay?
Yeah.
I'm good.
I actually feel a lot better
than before.
Also, this is kinda strange,
but my stomach feels warm
and sort of fuzzy.
[shrieks]
[CREATURE yells]
Hello, there,
and welcome to the land
of magic, Granvania!
Wow, what's this?
Some kind of toy with an A.I.
or a drone installed
or something?
Or could it maybe be a fairy?
I'm Mana!
Wonderful name, isn't it?
You're a virgin, aren't you?
You smell as fresh
as a bed of daisies!
Okay, I think I've had enough
of the rude toy now.
[MAN]
Mana,
are these the ones
you mentioned?
[MANA]
That's right, Nar.
These are our illustrious
Visitors this time.
And look!
They've already got the emblems!
Two Visitors at once, then.
How fascinating.
It's dangerous for you
to remain here.
Come, follow me.
Wait, where are we going?
To Castle Granvania.
I want the two of you
to meet our ruler.
He'll be glad to see you.
My name is Narcisstes,
by the way.
I'm a court scholar
for the Granvania Kingdom.
[ITSUKI] And, uh,
that's where we are now?
[NARCISSTES]
Yes. And in our world,
we refer to your world
as "Sola."
[MANA]
Let me explain.
You see, Granvania exists
in an entirely different
dimension than your own.
Many of the past Visitors
to our realm
have even referred to it
as a land of enchantment!
[ITSUKI] So, this world
and ours are parallel.
This is crazy.
[NARCISSTES]
I've brought them, your majesty.
[KING]
I'm very glad you're here.
I am the reigning
King of Granvania.
Call me Shangri-La.
I'm sure that the two of you
are more than a little shocked
and frightened
by this recent turn of events.
But if you would, I'd like you
to hear me out.
Yes, of course.
I am not going to mince words.
Our world is being threatened
as it never has been before.
For that reason,
I'm looking to both of you
to save it for us.
You want us to save the world?
Why do you want us?
Are you really serious?
You two have
been chosen as Visitors.
You see, in our world, every
ten years, new Visitors come.
They appear from the sky
with constellation emblems
on their skin.
You have a very special power.
I'd like you to use it to carry
out this mission for us.
Or rather, I should say you have
no choice but to do so.
Understand, your power
is the only thing
that can possibly
save our world.
Let's be clear.
Are you saying
that unless we save
this world for you,
we can't go home?
[SHANGRI-LA]
Indeed I am.
You're very perceptive.
This is nuts!
I mean, we're seriously average
high school students!
And you want us
to save the world?
I mean, all of this is
just really sudden
and unexpected, right?
Mahiru!
[SHANGRI-LA]
Take her to the doctor.
[NARCISSTES]
Yes, Your Majesty.
[MANA] You must be
pretty tired, as well.
Maybe you should go rest
in your room.
[ITSUKI]
Where'd Mahiru get taken?
[MANA]
Why? Do you get a little anxious
when she's not around?
You creeper.
Always after it!
[giggles]
I can only imagine the
shenanigans you've gotten up to.
"Oh no, we can't!
The family's home!
"Not like this!
"Let's keep today our secret.
"Just you and me, okay?"
[giggles]
The two of you canoodling
under the same roof!
I'm so envious,
you Visitervert!
What's a Visitervert?
She's fine, you know.
She's just resting
in the doctor's office now.
The doctor said she's
simply a bit exhausted,
nothing more.
That's good news.
[MANA] We'll continue
this talk tomorrow.
I'll bring some food up
to you later.
You've got real hottie
taking care of you now,
so you should be
grateful, you know!
What hottie? Where?
Feast your eyes, handsome!
Ah! You monster!
[GIRL 1] The honored Visitor
has finally appeared to us.
The time has now come
for me to fulfill
my solemn duty.
[GIRL 2] I really shouldn't.
They're so good, though!
[yelps]
[gasps]
What the hell is this?
Huh.
Your body's nicer than expected.
I actually feel encouraged
about entrusting you
with the fate of our world.
Huh?
Oh. No, don't worry.
I won't be
taking your underwear off.
What's this?
Is it just me
or are you disappointed?
Maybe a little.
I'm the court doctor.
My name's Reone.
Itsuki.
I want you to take a good look
at your body.
You'll notice, you now
bear emblems
representing all twelve
constellations.
See?
These mark you as a Visitor.
Physical proof.
What's next?
I mean, what are we
supposed to do now?
You're willing to
help us, then?
If it's the only way
to get back home,
we have no choice.
I know Mahiru wants
to return, too.
[REONE] Once you complete
your mission,
the gate of light
should appear to you again.
A Visitor's duty is to enter
the labyrinth
and quiet
the Impurities within.
Impurities?
The Impurities of the labyrinth
have turned into monsters.
They're extremely dangerous.
Did you say "monsters?"
[REONE] And at the deepest layer
of the labyrinth,
you'll find
the Lord Impurity.
It can't be defeated
by those of this world.
I'm sad to say, history
has already proven that for us.
[ITSUKI]
So how do I defeat it?
You'll retrieve the Star Wards
who have lost their power
from the labyrinth.
In addition, you will also need
to produce new ones.
That way, the labyrinth
will be able to contain
the Impurities again.
Star Wards, huh?
Look at this to learn more.
Do your best to figure
it out as you go.
[ITSUKI]
But...
I'm just a normal human being.
I don't have the power
to fight monsters.
[REONE]
I beg to differ.
You're a Visitor.
You're the hero who's
destined to save this world.
Also, you'll never be alone.
To help ensure that you're
a success,
the twelve priestesses will be
joining you on your mission.
[MANA] The twelve maidens
are chosen at birth
for their ability
to purify Impurities!
They aid the Visitor,
and using their special ability,
they're able to create a Star
Ward of their own constellation.
And until it loses its power,
they fulfill
their designated duties
as priestesses of our realm.
Not only that...
but she's one of them.
Huh?
May I introduce you?
This is the priestess of Virgo.
[ITSUKI]
Mahiru?
I was given
the exact same story.
As crazy as it is, it seems I'm
a Visitor who was summoned here
as the priestess of Virgo.
Tell me this.
Did your body
expel anything
around the same time
that emblem surfaced?
Yeah, it did.
I actually threw up.
Honestly, thinking about it
makes me feel
a little gross again.
When one is chosen
to be a priestess,
she expels any Impurities
she's born with from her body.
Depending on the person,
they can sometimes develop
symptoms similar to pregnancy.
Oh, wow.
Does that mean...
Yes, you should be fine now.
After all, it sounds like you've
already expelled the Impurity.
What a relief!
So, I wasn't really
pregnant after all.
[MANA]
The priestess has
one other very important task
to perform.
And that's the Love Ritual!
Dude, are you joking?
[MANA] The twelve
priestesses themselves
cannot stand directly
against Impurities!
So, instead, they take
on the duty
of giving birth
to your children.
My what?
[MANA]
That's right!
You and the priestesses
will be joined
to give birth
to a Star Child!
So get ready, Visitor!
Let's set that course
for intercourse!
Did you say intercourse?
[squeals]
[MANA] Come on, don't pretend
you don't know.
It's relations between a man
and a woman!
Coitus, copulation,
a nighttime rendezvous,
bumping uglies,
intimacy,
a tryst, fornication,
getting it on, a carnal embrace!
A hookup! A booty call!
In other words, sex!
Come on, admit it,
we all love sex!
Just say it!
I mean, yeah, who doesn't?
[MANA] The Star Children
are the only ones
capable of purifying Impurities,
with the Visitor's help.
In other words, you
making babies is a crucial act
that will ensure
this world's safety,
and it's a proven strategy
that'll dictate all our fates!
Typical courtships
can't even touch this!
This love will save the world!
That said,
being surrounded
by twelve beauties
means you'll have
a literal harem!
Fantastic right?
Bet you're already drooling.
Actions speak a little
louder than words, though.
What do you say we have you
perform the Love Ritual here
and create the first Star Child?
-[grunts]
-This is perfect.
You can practice
with your lovely Mahiru.
It'll be easier for you
if the first time is
-with someone you know.
-[gasps]
Don't worry. I'll teach you
how to carry out the ritual
and you will love it.
Hang on a second, Doctor Reone!
You want us to...
Right now?
It's all right.
You'll get used to it.
What?
I sure hope not!
Hey, don't worry.
It only hurts at first,
you know.
You'll feel great after a while.
"This is amazing!
"I've never felt
anything like it!"
Remember, you're doing
this to return to your world.
It's the only way.
Itsuki, this is her first time,
so try to be
as gentle as possible.
Of course.
Well, let's begin, then.
♪
What a weird day,
am I right?
[ITSUKI] What kind
of ritutal is this?
[MAHIRU]
I guess...
we have to do this in order
to get back home, don't we?
[ITSUKI]
Seems that way.
This is really
overwhelming, though.
I mean, I've thought
about my first time a lot,
just like anyone would.
About the right person
and place.
I'm so sorry.
Don't be!
I wasn't trying to say
I hate the idea
of being with you.
The truth is,
losing my virginity
to you would be
okay with me.
Although, doing it with
a room full of people watching
isn't quite
what I envisioned for myself.
And doing it to get
pregnant seems totally crazy.
The Love Ritual isn't
exactly the same
as procreating,
to be fair.
The Star Children arise
without any discomfort
for the priestess.
They just pop forth!
It's easy!
Don't worry.
"Pop?"
[MANA] It's okay to be
a little nervous!
The trick is to just
jump right in!
Test it out!
So start trying!
How 'bout right now?
Just a little.
Just the tip!
Please?
Pervert!
What do you think
you're doing?
I'm here to look after Itsuki.
All right, first things first,
off with the fancy underwear!
And I think we should show him
your birthday suit,
while we're at it!
[MAHIRU]
No!
[MANA] Come on, Itsuki!
Get over here!
What are you waiting for?
Oh, so plump and smooth,
just perfect for fondling!
It'd be such a waste not to
get in here and get it on!
Why the hell are you
this strong
when you're just
a freakin' toy?
Hey, what are you doing?
[ITSUKI]
Mahiru wants you to stop.
[MANA shrieks]
You should know,
your feelings and comfort
are the first priority
for me right now.
I appreciate it.
That said, when I think
of everything
that's happened here so far,
the only thing I can think to do
is what they've asked,
so we can go home.
I don't want you to force it.
But...
In order to fulfill
our mission,
I'm asking you now
to have my child.
[gasps]
Um... sorry.
This is so we can...
go home.
Be gentle, okay?
[MANA vocalizing]
[WOMAN]
You want to watch?