‐What is the status?
‐The area’s been expanding
at a constant rate
since we first
started monitoring it.
The Stealth Force has been
dispatched to investigate.
They should arrive at the
Outer Barrier momentarily.
‐I just established contact.
They’ll be passing by the Dangai
Precipice World in 10 seconds.
They’re about to enter
the dimensional area.
Opening communication lines.
MALE SPEAKER (ON
VIDEO PHONE SCREEN):
Hey, what the‐‐
where’s the exit?
It’s no good.
We can’t break through,
and the Stealth Force
is unable to
infiltrate the area.
What the hell’s going on?
Requesting immediate backup.
‐We’ve got them.
We’ve got you backup.
Maintain your positions.
‐This is the Research
Technology Concept.
Insertion into the
dimensional area has failed.
The Stealth Force is on the‐‐
‐Notify Central 46
of the situation.
Let’s get them out of there.
MALE SPEAKER (ON VIDEO PHONE
SCREEN): It’s the current.
The restricted
current is too strong.
‐Listen, help is on the way.
Now tell us, what
prevented you from entering
the dimensional area?
MALE SPEAKER (ON VIDEO
PHONE SCREEN): Aaah!
‐I think that guy was born
with extra hands or something.
[panting]
[roaring]
[loud crash]
‐What is that, dust?
‐It just happened.
‐It’s coming right at us.
‐Get ready.
‐Right.
‐Hey, hold on.
‐Where are you going?
[theme music]
‐Back off.
Aaah!
‐Ichigo.
‐What’s up?
‐Here we go.
‐That Hollow was
chasing this girl.
So it’s a good thing we
came along when we did.
‐Hmm.
‐Don’t worry.
It’s all right.
He only looked scary.
‐Would you just‐‐ It’s
time for you to go.
‐It’s going to be
all right you’re
going to like the Soul Society.
It’s not scary at all.
It’s where departed
souls go to live.
‐But I‐‐
‐You don’t want to
hang around this place.
What if another one of those
monsters comes after you?
‐Is it over already?
‐Yeah.
Thanks a lot.
You know, Ichigo‐‐
‐What is it?
‐You use your combat
pass too much.
‐Huh?
What are you talking about?
[grunt] What the hell was that?
Blah.
‐Somehow you always
forget that you have him.
You think you can leave
your Gigai lying around
wherever you want.
Then I get stuck making
excuses afterwards.
‐What do you mean?
‐Here’s an example.
Someone happens to walk by.
Oh, dear me, is something wrong?
This man’s not breathing.
What do I do?
An ambulance?
That won’t do any good
if he’s already dead.
Someone better call a hearse.
You see what I mean?
‐Yeah.
Like they never call a hearse.
‐That’s not the point.
The point is whenever you
leave your body lying around,
there’s always a big commotion.
‐There’s no pulse.
He’s in cardiac arrest.
‐I rest my case.
‐Hey, my body.
‐Aah.
‐It’s so sad.
‐Oh, look, he’s coming to.
‐Look at that.
‐What’s going on?
‐How‐‐
‐What’s up?
‐Are you all right?
‐Oh, god.
‐Hold still, will you?
Easy.
‐What are you doing?
‐Let go of me.
RUKIA: Oh, please.
‐Ah, that really sucked.
‐Now who was it that
was just saying that?
You’re lucky I had
my memory replacement
to switch everyone’s memory.
Kon.
‐Hello, hello.
‐What the hell?
‐You’re the one who
needs to have him around,
so you hold him.
‐I don’t want to
carry this thing.
‐Rukia, how could you do this?
‐You like that?
Huh?
Do ya?
Little bastard.
‐Wait.
Hold on.
What’s that smell?
ICHIGO: Shut up!
‐There’s a bunch of
dog poop down here.
ICHIGO: Well, I hope it stinks.
‐This doesn’t make sense.
What is it?
‐If it’s another Hollow,
then what are we waiting for?
Aaah.
You got that stuff in my mouth.
‐Ichigo.
‐It serves you right.
Now we’re even.
‐Hey!
‐I’ll be right with you
just as soon as I’m‐‐
‐Help.
[loud rumble]
‐The train station.
‐Hey!
What’s up with this
spiritual pressure?
‐I don’t know.
I’ve never felt this kind of
spiritual pressure before.
‐Huh?
‐Wow, what are these things?
‐Ooh, like ghosts.
‐No one else can see them.
They must be souls.
‐If they were, wouldn’t they
have chains on their chests?
It’s weird.
‐We have no choice.
‐Oh, well, here we go again.
‐Hey, put that away.
‐Fine.
Disgusting.
Kon, try to stay out of trouble.
Hey, you can’t
just leave me here.
Whoa, well, what are you doing?
Hey.
‐This is Rukia
Kuchiki, Squad 13,
World of the Living Area 3888.
‐What now?
‐Ichigo, see if you can
perform a Kenso on one of them.
‐Really?
A Kenso?
‐Reporting in.
We’ve encountered a large number
of unknown beings possessing
a strange spiritual pressure.
‐It doesn’t have any
effect on these guys.
‐Something’s going on.
All I’m getting is interference.
‐What’s going on?
‐Stop.
‐Rukia.
KON: Make way!
‐What’s with you guys?
Back off.
‐What should we do?
‐I don’t know.
Who’s that?
‐A Soul Reaper?
What are you doing here?
‐No, hey, get off, will ya?
Hmm?
Who’s that?
‐She’s going to
release her Shikai.
‐What?
‐Bring them to the twilight.
‐Ichigo.
‐Hold on a minute.
You don’t even know what
the hell you’re doing.
Those things aren’t Hollows,
so just back off, dammit.
‐Stay out of my way, you jerk.
‐What?
You stepped on my
face, you little brat.
‐Bring them to the twilight.
Mirokumaru.
‐Now what else could
possibly go wrong?
Huh?
What happened to that other guy?
‐Sorry I’m late.
Can you believe how
strong that wind was?
‐Any idea what just happened?
‐They vanished.
‐That was awesome.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And it felt so good.
‐Oh, great.
It’s the jerk.
‐Aah.
It was you.
Hold on.
How’d you change into
your Gigai so fast?
‐I don’t know.
‐You better tell me who you are.
‐I’m a Soul Reaper.
‐I already know that,
but who are you?
‐If you want to
know someone’s name,
it’s best to introduce
yourself first.
‐I’m Ichigo Kurosaki.
‐See?
That wasn’t so hard.
And my name’s Senna.
Later.
‐You’re not going anywhere,
not until you tell me
why you did that?
‐Because it’s my job.
‐What were those
things back there,
and what did you do to them?
‐Aah.
‐What?
Are those things back again?
‐This is bad.
I knew it.
‐What do you mean?
‐Hmm.
Nope, yellow just
isn’t my color.
‐What difference does it make?
Come on.
‐Your name’s Ichigo?
‐Yeah.
‐Check it out.
‐Huh?
‐There’s an unconscious man
in front of the train station.
Requesting an
ambulance immediately.
‐Hey, you OK?
‐Not again.
‐You really ought to
take care of that.
‐Oh, no, you’re coming with me.
w let’s go.
‐Hey, take it easy.
‐I still got some questions.
‐He never learns.
‐Aah.
Give up yet?
‐You got to be kidding.
‐I don’t know.
You really think it’s
wise for a lieutenant
to be drinking in the
middle of the day?
‐What, are you crazy?
I could drink this all
day and not feel a thing.
It looks like it’s
empty already.
‐What?
Not again.
You guzzled it all,
you drunken geezer.
‐You want to make
something of it, cue ball?
‐Damn straight.
Come on, I’m going to
teach you a lesson.
‐Fine.
Whoever loses buys
the Sake, got it?
‐Try to take the
high ground, huh?
‐It’s always better
to be on top.
‐Yeah.
We’ll see.
Here I‐‐
‐Lose your nerve?
‐What is that thing?
‐Huh?
‐You guys, look.
A Ferris Wheel.
I’ve always wanted to
ride on one of those.
Wow.
Sorry.
What is it that
you wanted to know?
‐What squad do you belong to?
‐I can never keep track
of all the little details.
I know that I belong
to one of those squads.
‐Now, listen, we’ve seen
you handle a Zanpakuto,
and you know how to release it.
Only a Soul Reaper would
have that knowledge.
You must be in a squad.
Every Soul Reaper
belongs to a squad.
How can you not remember that?
‐Question, please.
Before we go any further,
what are you doing here?
‐Well, I’m here
because‐‐ hey, wait.
‐So I forgot.
What’s the big deal?
I don’t see what
difference it makes.
‐Can you at least tell us what
those guys were back there?
‐I haven’t the slightest idea.
Ooh, he’s so cute.
Can I pet him?
‐Sure.
‐I just had this feeling that
I should get rid of them,
you know?
Instinct.
Isn’t that what they call it?
‐Whacko.
‐Listen, Ichigo, I need to
go back to the Soul Society.
‐Huh?
‐I’m having trouble
contacting them.
I think they should know
about that phenomenon
we witnessed earlier.
Stay with that girl, and don’t
let her out of your sight.
‐Hey, you can’t leave
me with that nutcase.
‐Wow, Rukia.
‐Don’t mess this up.
‐Boy, what’s she
so uptight about?
‐Hey, Ichigo.
Shut up you idiot.
There are people around.
‐She’s gone.
‐Huh?
Dammit.
Hey.
‐You’re so persistent.
‐Wait.
What a pain.
Hey.
‐Oh. [giggle] Remember
when you told me
that if I answered
your questions,
you’d do anything
I asked you to?
‐No, I never said
anything like that.
‐Let’s play tag, you’re it.
‐Wait.
I don’t want to play.
Hey.
Wait up.
I don’t believe this.
Senna.
Come on out.
This isn’t funny.
‐Hey.
What’s with all
the fun and games?
‐Rangiku.
Toshiro.
‐It’s been a while.
Refer to me as Captain
Hitsugaya, and not Toshiro.
‐Fine.
What are you two
doing here anyway?
‐Wait up, you guys.
‐We need to talk.
‐Yeah, well, uh,
I’m kind of busy.
‐Just come with us.
‐No, wait.
Hey.
Dammit.
I got to go, but
I’ll be right back.
Don’t go anywhere.
‐Mommy, that man is
talking to himself.
‐I see.
So Rukia went back
to the Soul Society.
Sounds as if you
just missed her.
‐Well, then, I suppose you
might as well get started.
‐At 12:50 AM today, a town
from the World of the Living
suddenly appeared
above the Seireitei.
We also detected a trail
of spiritual waves flowing
into the World of the Living.
Shortly after that, we
lost all communication
between our two worlds.
‐So what’s it all mean?
‐This guy is clueless.
‐Just relax.
Allow me to clarify a
few of these concepts.
You see our universe
has two worlds, which
are the World of the
Living where we are,
and the Soul Society.
Between them is the
Dangai Precipice World,
which serves as the tunnel,
as well as its main purpose
to keep the two
worlds from colliding.
See?
You went through it one
time, or have you forgotten?
It doesn’t matter.
At any rate, about three
days ago, a new dimension
appeared between
the Dangai Precipice
World and the World
of the Living.
It began to expand
rapidly bridging the gap
and adhering to both worlds.
At this point, it appears that
the area that attached itself
is acting like a lens.
Now you see, the
World of the Living
looks as if it’s located
within the Soul Society, which
is in a different dimension.
In other words, it just
looks like a mirage.
‐The Stealth Force was
sent out to investigate
this newly created
dimension, but they failed.
So now, we’re investigating
the influx of spiritual waves
into the World of the Living.
It was decided that I would
head up the operation.
‐Hold on a minute.
Why were you picked?
‐Because all the other
captains backed out.
‐Let’s just stick
to the details.
‐That must’ve been what
those white things were.
‐You saw something unusual?
‐Yeah, there were these
white ghostly things.
Must have been hundreds of them
wearing these red pointy hats.
‐It sounds like Blanks.
‐And that means the
Valley of Screams.
‐Time for explanation
number two.
Ready, Tessai?
‐Uh‐huh.
‐As you already
know, souls migrate
between the World of the
Living and the Soul Society.
From time to time,
however, there
are souls who for some
reason become detached
from the Cycle of
Transmigration while
in the Dangai Precipice World.
These souls wander aimlessly
through the Dangai Precipice
World and are slowly drawn
together over a period of time.
As the souls come together, it
causes a new dimension, hence,
the Valley of Screams.
In the Valley of
Screams, the souls
separate into memory
and energy, then
return to the Cycle
of Transmigration.
Are you following me so far?
‐Yeah, I got it.
‐So Ichigo, from the
description you gave,
it sounds as if
what you witnessed
were Blanks, which are
souls with no memories.
‐What happens to the memories?
They must go somewhere.
l, they merge
together into one entity
and return to the
World of the Living.
It’s called a Shinenju.
It’s a jewel that acts as
a collection of memories.
In any case, the appearance
of the Valley of Screams,
in itself, isn’t a
matter for concern.
It’s a natural and
common phenomenon.
Yet, there is a problem.
This time the Valley of Screams
has connected the Soul Society
to the World of the
Living, something
which has never happened before.
‐It’s not just some
weird natural phenomena?
‐There has never been
a natural phenomena
that has created a tunnel
linking two worlds.
That’s what’s going on here.
There’s no doubt that someone’s
doing this deliberately.
‐Hey.
That’s right.
‐Kon, what are you doing?
There was some guy wearing
really strange armour standing
right in the middle of
all those white things.
I saw it myself.
‐In a strange armour?
‐Do you remember any specific
details about the amour?
‐Of course, I’ve got a
memory like a steel trap.
Uh, now let’s see.
It was kind of a, uh, hmm,
well, when you think about it,
it was more of a‐‐
‐I’ll just take
this and analyze it.
‐Yes, please do.
If it’s being done
intentionally,
I doubt that whoever’s behind
this has honorable motives.
So what do they want?
At this point, it’s difficult
to know with any certainty.
‐But still, I have this feeling.
It concerns the Shinenju.
It must have returned to
the World of the Living,
and that’s what they want.
That theory makes
the most sense.
We’ll analyze the data and
try to identify the enemy.
I want you to keep watch
over the town, Ichigo.
I’m certain it’s
only a matter of time
before they appear again.
While you’re at it, keep your
eyes open for the Shinenju.
‐Yeah, no problem.
Ah.
Sorry about that.
Why’d she still be
hanging around here?
‐Wow, you came back
just like you said.
I’m right over here.
‐Would you quit messing around?
It’s time to answer
some questions.
Fine, you catch me, and I’ll
tell you whatever you want.
‐What?
Hey.
What’d I just say?
Dammit.
GAME HOST: He will now
drink an entire gallon
of orange soda in
two seconds flat.
Ready, and go.
‐10, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four, three, two‐‐
‐It’s all gone.
‐Give him a big hand, folks.
‐But he drank it too fast.
‐And you know what happens
when you get it wrong, right?
‐[shout] Yeah.
GAME HOST: Thank you very much.
Thank you.
If you enjoyed the
show, please feel
free to show your appeciation.
Pass the hat.
‐There’s a girl on
the roof over there.
‐Dammit, Senna.
‐Look.
‐Yeah, oh yeah.
‐Look at that girl.
‐Huh?
‐What’s she doing up there?
‐It must be some kind of act.
‐This feels so nice.
‐Where’d she go?
‐She disappeared.
No, wait, there she is.
‐Ta‐da.
All right.
‐Pretty good, isn’t she?
‐Come on, take a bow.
‐Yeah, right.
Thanks.
‐Aah.
‐Oh, come on, now.
They completely upstaged us.
‐That’s show business.
SENNA: Thanks, it looks great.
You could have saved
us both a lot of time.
If you said you were treating,
I’d have answered right away.
‐So let me get this straight.
You don’t have any money?
OK.
What do you know about them?
‐Who are you talking about?
‐I just explained it to you.
The Blanks and the
Shinenju, remember?
You need to tell me
everything you know.
‐I would if I could.
It’s the first
I’ve heard of them.
So someone’s using those pointy
hat things try and find this,
uh, this Shinen‐a‐ma‐bob?
‐Shinenju.
‐Right.
They’re using them to find it?
‐Yeah.
‐So who is this someone?
‐That’s what we’re
trying to figure out.
‐And then what will you do?
‐I’m not quite sure.
‐Have you got any idea what
the Shinen thingy looks like?
‐Not a clue.
‐You’re not making this easy.
Well, it sounds to
me like you’re just
going to have to wait
for those pointy hat guys
to show up again.
You know what?
I’m going to help you out.
‐Huh?
‐There’s just one condition.
‐I knew it.
‐First, we got to do that.
‐Huh?
‐Take me for a ride
on that, and I’ll
help you with whatever you want.
‐I’m not falling for that again.
What the‐‐ Just what is
it with you and heights?
‐I don’t know.
I like it when I’m way up high.
All the things that seem
confusing or messed up suddenly
become clear.
‐Hey.
That ribbon.
‐Oh, you noticed.
The red looks better than
the yellow, don’t you think?
‐Yeah, but how’d you
get it with no money?
‐I wandered into some
shop to look at stuff
and tried this on to
see if I liked it.
I guess I must have
forgot I had it on.
It happens all the time.
‐Not when I’m around.
‐Well, wait, aren’t you
going to pay the check?
‐I’d like to buy this.
‐Ah, a present for
your girlfriend?
‐My sister.
‐Shall I gift wrap it for you?
‐Thanks, but I’m
kind of in a hurry.
‐Thank you very much.
I hope she likes it.
‐Here, take it.
‐I can’t believe you
actually did that.
You’re so uptight.
‐I hate that kind of thing.
Just take it and shut up.
‐Thanks so much, Ichigo.
Now the Ferris Wheel.
‐Yeah, right, forget about it.
‐Meany.
‐We high schoolers aren’t
exactly made out of money,
you know.
‐Hmm.
‐Hey.
‐I’m going to the restroom.
Is that all right with you?
He’s not a bad guy once
you get to know him.
Sweet.
All right.
That river.
‐Daddy!
Welcome home, Daddy.
Aah.
Dad?
‐Is my little boy, hungry?
‐Yes, Daddy.
‐Here you go.
‐Cheers, everyone.
‐Come on.
This place was so
crowded a minute ago.
‐Oh.
This is‐‐ this is my‐‐
this is my funeral?
Mom, Dad.
Aaah!
What?
Who are you?
‐You’ve got better
reflexes than I expected.
‐Why are you here?
And what do you want?
‐I’m going to be your escort.
Our commander, Ganryu, has
issued orders to summon you.
‐He summoned me?
Who is this guy?
I’ve never heard of him.
‐That information
is unimportant.
So what are you
going to do about it?
‐Jai, I told you not
to waste time talking.
‐You should know better
than to jump out like that.
‐This will only take a second.
Stop it.
That tickles.
‐Don’t crush her.
‐We’re already late, let’s go.
‐Ah, ah.
‐Now, let’s go, shall we?
‐Hold it.
Where do you think you’re going?
‐Who the hell are you anyway?
Aaah, oh, my arm.
My arm.
‐What’s with all
the wandering off?
‐I just‐‐ why don’t you
mind your own business?
‐Afraid I can’t do that.
At least not until
you’ve kept your promise.
Hey, big guy.
Sorry about the arm.
‐You’re going to pay for that.
I’m gonna kick your ass.
‐That’s enough.
Patience.
The time has not yet come.
‐The time?
What’s he talking about?
‐Dammit.
‐Hey, wait a minute.
Hey, what’s the big idea of
letting me pay for lunch,
and then running away.
‐I wasn’t running away.
‐Then what were you doing?
‐My entire family is
buried in this cemetery.
‐You expect me to believe that?
‐I’m telling the truth.
I remember it all.
I do.
I remember when I was alive,
though it’s still kind of hazy.
I had to come and
see for myself.
My house used to be
around here, too.
Tell you what.
Let’s pick this up tomorrow.
I promise I’ll help you.
All right?
‐You idiot.
I’m not going to abandon
someone who was just attacked.
‐I don’t know about
this bad guy story.
It just sounds fishy.
‐Yeah, I know it sounds
pretty wild, but it’s true.
And it’s just for one night.
‐I’m Senna.
‐My name’s Yuzu.
It’s a pleasure to meet you.
‐Thanks for having me.
‐Hey, Yuzu, you
don’t mind if she
sleeps in your room
tonight, do you?
And she probably wants a bath.
‐OK.
‐What’s the matter
with you, Dad?
‐You guys are both crazy.
‐You can hang out in here
until your bed’s ready.
‐Hmm, boy’s rooms are
always so drab and boring.
‐Gimme a break.
‐Whatever.
It seems like you’ve got
a nice family, though.
‐You think?
‐Yeah, my dad was way different.
‐Hey.
‐What?
‐Is something wrong?
‐Hmm, nothing at all.
‐So do you have
any ideas as to why
those guys wanted
to take you away?
Did they say anything?
‐Oh, I think the guy said
commander Gan somebody wanted
me be brought to him.
‐Yeah, and what else?
‐That was it.
If you hadn’t come by when you
did, I might have learned more.
‐You’re crazy.
Hey, what are you doing?
You can’t sleep in here.
‐There’s nothing wrong with it.
‐Are you kidding?
Hey, quit kicking
your legs around,
and put your shoes back on.
‐That’s not cool, you guys.
‐Shh.
She says she’s going
to sleep in his bed.
‐So what?
It’s not like he’s a little kid.
‐No.
‐Oh, Masaki, it’s the
day we’ve been dreading.
I don’t know what
I’m supposed to do.
‐What’s going on out here?
‐I told you it wasn’t cool.
‐The bath is ready
whenever she is.
‐You guys.
Hey, Senna.
You can take your bath now.
Hey.
URAHARA (ON PHONE):
Ichigo it’s me, Urahara.
How’s it going?
Find anything out
about the Shinenju?
‐Nothing yet, but
I had a little run
in with those guys
Kon was talking about.
Remember them?
URAHARA (ON PHONE):
Are you all right?
‐Yeah, it wasn’t a big deal.
They took off before
anything happened.
‐Glad to hear it.
Listen, one of the
reasons I called
is because we were able to turn
up a few things on our end.
‐Like what?
URAHARA (ON PHONE): We
were able to analyze
the visions taken
from Kon’s memories.
If you recall, Kon said he saw
someone wearing strange armour
in the middle of the Blanks.
We identified the armour as
belonging to a group that was
banished from the Soul Society
after their takeover attempt
failed.
So I think we can be fairly
certain their motive is
revenge.
The question remains,
why are they here,
and what do they want?
‐Kisuke, can I ask
you a question?
URAHARA (ON PHONE): What is it?
‐Well, is it possible
for a Soul Reaper
to have memories of
when they were alive?
‐Huh?
I’ve never heard
of that happening.
You want to tell me
what this is about?
‐Nah, I was just
wondering, that’s all.
‐Hey, do you really think those
things will show up here again?
‐I’m not sure.
All I know is that the Blanks
showed up here once, and right
now that’s the only
clue we’ve got.
‐Man, this is totally boring.
‐I don’t remember this many
people being here at this hour.
Usually, things
are pretty quiet.
Not much going on.
Hey, Senna, do me a
favor and stay close, OK?
Hey.
Senna!
Where’d you go?
‐Over here.
‐In case you forgot, you
just got attacked yesterday.
You can’t just go
wandering off like that.
[crying] A soul?
What is it, kid.
What’s the problem?
‐You’re scaring him.
Hey, there, big guy.
My name’s Senna.
What’s yours?
‐Tomoya.
That’s a really nice name.
If you want to tell me what’s
wrong, maybe I can help.
‐I’m lost, and I’m all alone
because my Dad is gone.
‐Were you going someplace
with your father?
‐Uh‐huh.
We were in the car, and he
was taking me to the festival.
But I fell asleep, and when
I woke up, he was gone.
‐I see.
‐I know you miss your Dad.
And I’m sure he misses you, too.
But your Dad is up
in heaven right now.
‐Uh‐huh, he’s not in heaven.
My Dad is looking
for me right now.
I know it.
‐Well, if he is,
then maybe Ichigo
and I can come along with
you and help you find him.
‐Yeah.
‐We’ll all find him together.
OK, now, which way
did you come from?
‐Over that way.
‐Then let’s get going.
‐Hey.
Actually, we’re kind
of busy right now.
‐You said yourself
we have no leads.
No sense in hanging around here.
Let’s go.
‐Yeah.
‐How much longer are we
going to keep this up?
It’s pretty obvious there’s
no festival around here.
Besides, those no guarantee his
father’s still on this side.
‐We are going to find him.
There’s not much time left until
he has to leave this world.
And then, that
little boy is going
to have a long
journey ahead of him.
This will be his very last wish.
Think how sad it would be
if it didn’t come true?
I can’t bring myself to
perform a Konso like this.
I just want‐‐ I want to give
him that one last good memory.
‐Senna.
I’m coming.
‐Hurry up.
I found it.
Come on.
I don’t see him.
Where is he?
‐We’ll find him.
Come on.
‐OK.
‐I’m so glad this
place is still here.
We came here a lot when
I was a little girl.
‐But you‐‐
‐Tomoya!
‐Huh?
‐Tomoya.
‐It’s Daddy.
Daddy, oh.
‐I’m so sorry.
I’m so sorry, Tomoya.
‐I never thought
we’d really find him.
‐Thank you so much.
‐See?
We did it.
‐Uh‐huh.
‐It’s all thanks to you.
Ah, no, please, I didn’t
do anything, really.
‐It’s hard to believe.
I guess you were so wrapped
up in helping Tomoya
that you didn’t even
notice all the souls who
are gathered here.
I was able to find this
place, thanks to them.
‐All these people led you here?
‐Yeah.
Don’t you understand?
They’re here because of you.
I’m surprised you didn’t know.
If it wasn’t for you,
they wouldn’t be here.
‐Tomoya, it’s time
for us to be going.
Bye, bye.
‐Hey.
Wait a minute.
Are these guys‐‐?
‐Why me?
Why?
Why are they all
attracted to me?
Ichigo.
I think that I must
be‐‐ is it true?
‐Senna.
Captain Ukitake, what
are you all doing here?
Rukia.
What’s this about?
‐Ichigo.
‐We’re here to carry out a
level one order from Central 46.
You’re to hand over
the girl immediately.
‐What?
‐Ichigo, I’ve searched every
record of the 13 Court Guard
Squads, the Stealth
Force and the Kido Force,
as well as the Soul
Reaper Academy.
There is no Senna
listed anywhere.
I also verified that the
Zanpakuto the girl uses,
Mirokumaru, was swallowed up
by the restrictive current
in the Dangai Precipice
World 100 years ago
along with its owner.
In other words, there is no
way her Zanpakuto can exist.
‐But that’s not possible.
What you’re saying isn’t true.
I am a Soul Reaper.
I know it.
‐Then when did you come to
the World of the Living?
How long ago?
‐It’s so confusing.
I remember walking
out by the banks
of that river two days ago.
And I’m not confused
about my name.
I know it’s Senna.
I remember that river.
When I was a little girl,
I‐‐ but I‐‐ then I was alone,
and there was no one else.
‐Don’t you see?
All those different memories
are mixed up in your head.
‐I know it’s hard to
comprehend, but the very thing
we’ve been searching for,
this Shinenju is actually you.
‐Is it true?
‐The Valley of Screams
became visible 24 hours ago.
We’ve concluded that the
man behind is Ganryu.
His motive is to
destroy the worlds.
In order to achieve
his objective,
he intends to
utilize the Shinenju.
The Shinenju Senna.
By order of the Soul Society, we
will now take you into custody.
‐But‐‐ but what
gives you the right?
What have I done?
I’m just one person.
How could‐‐
‐Just hold on.
You can’t do this.
‐Ichigo, what are you doing?
‐No matter what this girl is,
it doesn’t change the fact
that she exists at this moment.
Look, she has
feelings and emotions,
and has thoughts and
dreams just like you do.
But you want to ignore all
that and lock her away, right?
As far as I’m concerned,
you’re no different than them.
So you might as well
forget about it,
because I’m not handing
her over to you.
‐Sorry, but we haven’t the time
to debate this with you now,
Ichigo.
‐Step away!
Move Ichigo.
‐I can’t do that.
‐What is that?
‐Renji.
‐Matsumoto.
‐Damn.
Not these again.
Hey, kid.
It wasn’t time for us
before, but it is now.
‐Yeah, you’re right.
It’s time to lose
your other arm.
‐Ichigo.
‐Kon, take care of her.
‐Right.
‐I don’t know what
happened, but he’s
got more power than yesterday.
‐Go.
Get the Shinenju.
‐Yes, ma’am.
Reign over the frosted
heavens, Hyorinmaru.
‐Now roar, Zabimaru!
What the hell?
‐Sogyonokotowari.
Go Kuchchiki.
‐Right.
You get out of here, you freaks.
‐Rukia.
‐Hado 33, Sokatsui.
Get off me.
Wait.
‐I’m a Soul Reaper.
I’ll show them.
Aaah.
Bring them to the twilight.
‐No, don’t, Senna.
Senna.
‐There’s no mistaking it.
No.
That amour belongs
to the banished clan,
the noble House of Ryodoji.
‐I wouldn’t know about that.
We are from the Clan of
Darkness, the Dark One.
‐What?
Not so fast.
‐There’s no need to stay.
‐All right, put
the girl down now.
‐Hey, let go of me!
‐Senna.
I’ll handle this.
Forget it.
You can have her.
It’s over.
‐Ichigo.
Ichigo!
[scream]
‐Ichigo.
Ichigo.
‐He’s OK.
‐Oh.
Thanks.
I appreciate all of you
coming to help so quickly.
‐They didn’t even
slow those guys down.
‐Hey, it’s not that easy.
Remember, three squad captains
were present during the attack,
and even they were ineffective.
So it wasn’t his fault.
‐That’s true.
‐Tell me what happened.
‐Unfortunately, they had
planned an escape route,
and they were able to get away.
‐Have you been able to
learn anything else?
‐Yes, it appears that they plan
to use the Shinenju to draw
the World of the Living and
the Soul Society together.
The massive collision
would be devastating.
‐But why?
What do they want?
‐That I don’t know.
But it all points
towards that conclusion.
‐What about the Soul Society?
‐They’re in council right now
working on a plan of action.
Although, the
Valley of Screams is
completely inaccessible
from the Soul Society.
Without an entryway, it’s
impossible to mount an attack.
‐But still, there
must be some way in.
‐Well, I imagine the Shinenju
created some sort of passageway
into the World of the Living.
did get here somehow.
‐Yeah, that’s right.
‐Ichigo.
If we find the entrance,
we can go after them.
It is possible, isn’t it?
‐Uh‐huh.
‐Then let’s go.
‐Ichigo.
‐Hmm.
‐All right then.
I guess we’d better
start looking.
‐Right.
‐There’s absolutely no trace
of gun powder or chemical
residue left by the explosion.
‐What the hell is going on?
‐Ichigo.
I never should have‐‐
‐It’s not your fault, Rukia.
You did what you felt was right.
Senna is strong‐willed, and
stubborn, and a little crazy,
but she was trembling.
She was so frightened
and confused.
She had no idea
who she really was.
And I just couldn’t see that.
I failed and wasn’t
able to protect her.
‐Ah, you noticed.
The red looks better than
the yellow, don’t you think?
Remember when you told me that
if I answered your questions,
you’d do anything
I asked you to?
I don’t know.
I like it when I’m way up high.
All the things that seem
confusing or messed up suddenly
become clear.
‐I don’t get it.
Why’d she say that?
‐Ichigo.
What’s wrong?
‐Don’t worry.
Just come with me.
‐All right.
SENNA (VOICEOVER): I
remember when I was alive,
though it’s still kind of hazy.
My house used to be
around here, too.
‐There it is.
Right in the middle
of the river.
Jump.
‐What is that?
Look at that.
It’s the same phenomenon that’s
visible from the Soul Society.
‐I’m going in.
Rukia, contact Urahara and
tell him that we found it.
‐No.
It’s not safe.
Wait for the others.
‐I’m going now.
Tell the others.
Go.
I’m going to save Senna.
‐No, Ichigo.
‐What is this place?
Why am I up here?
I thought you wanted me
to do something for you.
‐You don’t need to do
a thing except sit back
and be the instrument through
which we fulfill our dream.
‐What are you talking about?
Lord Ganryu is the rightful
ruler of the Soul Society.
So lower your voice and
address him properly
or else you’ll regret it.
‐Relax.
I’ve long since abandoned the
need for such formalities.
1,000 years have passed
since we were banished
by the unjust laws
of the Soul Society.
They exiled our clan
to wonder endlessly
in this Dangai Precipice World.
We survived by evading the
restrictive current which
swallows up everything
that touches it.
We discovered the
souls who had strayed
from the Cycle of
Transmigration and turned
into wandering ghosts in
the Dangai Precipice World.
We then learned to
use them as an energy
source for our own power.
The number of souls
is always constant.
And when these
souls, or Blanks who
have strayed from the
Cycle of Transmigration
reach a certain number,
they’re naturally
drawn together and
generate a dimension
known as the Valley of Screams.
Imagine a dimension
consisting entirely
of a compact mass of Blanks.
And at the same time, all the
memories of these lost souls
merge into one object and return
to the World of the Living.
That is the Shinenju.
The Shinenju is you.
‐However, the Blanks
cannot completely lose
their individuality.
Even though the Blanks are
basically empty vessels,
they still wander
for a time searching
for their lost memories.
This is where the
problem begins.
If the Shinenju is
placed at the center
of the Valley of
Screams, the proximity
will intensify the Blanks
desire to seek their memories.
This will drive them to rush
towards the creating a vacuum.
The result will lead to
the Valley of Screams
to constrict and cause
the Dangai Precipice World
to collapse, pulling the
Soul Society and the World
of the Living together
in a massive collision.
‐Is that possible?
‐I got to admit, it’s not
a very pleasant thought.
‐Least pleasant of all, is the
fact that it’s already begun.
‐Never mind all the details.
How much damage are
we talking about?
‐It’s difficult to say exactly.
But when two worlds that
aren’t meant to touch align,
it would certainly result
in the destruction of one,
if not both worlds.
‐But when?
How much time do we have?
‐Given my limited data, I
can’t establish a precise time.
But I would guess about an hour.
‐I’ll mobilize the
Punishment Force
to attack the Valley
of Screams immediately.
‐It’s useless.
There is no Senkaimon that
connects the Soul Society
to the Valley of Screams.
Therefore, we have
no way to enter.
There’s nothing our troops
can do to stop this.
‐The situation is critical.
Prepare the Kido
Cannon immediately.
We must destroy the
Valley of Screams
and the by firing
directly into its core.
‐But if we do that, we’ll
cause massive damage
and countless casualties
to both worlds.
‐I’m sorry, but we
have no other choice.
‐Let me through.
‐Stand back.
You’re not allowed inside.
‐How dare you interrupt.
This is a captain’s meeting.
Be gone.
‐My deepest apologies, sir.
I will gladly accept
any punishment later.
However, I have
crucial information,
and it’s imperative
that you hear it.
This substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki has discovered
an entryway to the Valley
of Screams through the World
of the Living, and has
gone there to rescue the .
I beseech you, please
send reinforcements
to assist Ichigo.
‐Ichigo.
How did he‐‐
‐I’m afraid I cannot
honor your request.
‐But why, captain?
Mind you, I am not taking the
substitute Soul Reaper’s skills
lightly.
However, we have only one hour.
And there is no guarantee
that the 13 Court Guard Squads
could enter the Valley of
Screams, defeat the enemy,
and rescue the in that time.
Do not think poorly of me.
This meeting is now over.
All squads will begin
emergency procedures.
Prepare the Kido Cannon.
‐I have‐‐
‐I’m going, too.
That crazy bastard.
I’m not about to let him
take all the glory again.
‐The Blanks are being
drawn to the just
as you said Lord Ganryu.
‐Of course.
Well, now.
We have a guest.
‐Senna.
I’m coming for you.
‐Have you returned
for another beating?
‐Give Senna back.
Just as the moment has arrived
for her to finally awaken
as the , because of you she
will be forced to endure
unimaginable pain and
fear as a human being.
‐Ichigo.
Oh, no.
Ichigo.
‐Hang on.
[screaming]
‐Yeah, you bastards.
‐Mr. Urahara, don’t you think we
should go after Ichigo in case
he needs our help?
‐It’s impossible.
The Valley of Screams is
somewhat similar to the Soul
Society.
It’s a spiritual world
where humans cannot go.
‐Rukia.
‐Renji.
‐So how’d it go?
‐No good.
They refuse to send anyone.
And they intend to use
the Kido Cannon to destroy
the entire Valley of Screams.
‐If they do that, what
will happen to Ichigo?
‐I’m not about to
let that happen.
We’re going in there
to finish the job,
and get Ichigo out of there
before they fire the Kido
Cannon.
‐Do you have a plan?
‐Don’t worry about it.
We’ll come up with something.
‐You wouldn’t stand a chance
going in by yourselves.
We’ve already put
the team together.
Now we’re going to deal
with this ourselves.
‐And I’m coming, too.
‐Would you quit fooling around?
Let’s go.
‐Right.
‐Please, Rukia, please
take care of Ichigo.
‐Don’t you worry.
‐That’s it.
I’ve had enough of this.
Kenpachi.
‐You might want to move.
‐Don’t worry about me.
‐What’s that?
‐It’s time to get
down to business.
‐But why are you‐‐
‐We’re not about to let you
have all the fun yourself.
‐Things have gotten
fairly dull lately,
so we thought we could
do with some amusement.
‐I said you might need some
help, and they all volunteered.
So never fear, the
cavalry is here.
‐Let’s do what you
came here to do.
‐What are we waiting for?
Let’s do this.
‐Right.
Extend, Hozukimaru.
Yeah.
‐Roar, Heiniko.
‐Raise your head, Wabisuke.
‐You stupid little‐‐ on
‐Huh?
What the hell’s going on?
‐Hey.
This isn’t what you’re
looking for, is it?
‐You little‐‐ It’s
too late little girl.
Goodbye.
[scream]
‐[grunt]
‐Huh?
‐How ridiculous.
Hide and seek’s not
my favorite game,
but I’m not too bad at it.
‐Uh‐oh.
Get ’em, Kenny.
‐Are you ready to
use that sword?
What do you know.
You just might turn out
to be fun after all.
‐Reign over the frozen
heavens, Hyorinmaru.
‐Hanging in there, huh kid?
You don’t seriously believe
your energy will outlast mine?
But I’m happy to keep it
up as long as you are.
Take this.
That didn’t take long.
‐Now Bankai.
Daiguren Hyourinamru.
‐‐[grunt] I can’t believe he
still has that kind of power
left.
What’s happening?
No.
[scream]
‐Third chant is in place.
Preparations for
firing are complete.
‐Research Technology
CommCenter reports
the target will pass out of the
critical range in five minutes.
‐Hmm.
Head Captain.
‐I understand.
I will wait until
the very last second.
However‐‐
‐I will never let you
take the Shinenju.
‐Ichigo, grab on.
‐Renji.
‐Go Ichigo.
‐You’re not going anywhere.
‐We’ll kill the two of
you, and then your friends.
‐What the‐‐
‐Senna!
You still foolishly believe
that you can save the Shinenju?
‐We’ll see who looks
foolish after I walk out
of here with Senna.
‐You’re too late.
The Shinenju has
already begun to merge
with the Valley of Screams.
No one can stop it now.
‐Shut up.
I’ve had enough of your crap.
I’m grabbing Senna and
taking her out of here.
‐You still don’t
seem to understand.
I told you, it’s useless.
Getsuga Tensho!
‐You little pest.
‐You finally showed
yourself, huh?
After I crush you, I’m going
to walk out of here with Senna.
‐Go ahead.
Bring it on.
Tensa Zangetsu.
‐For a millennium
our clan was forced
to scrape out an
existence, surviving only
by concealing ourselves in the
dank crevices of the Dangai
Precipice World.
Our hatred for the Soul
Society was the only fuel
that drove us to endure
that living hell.
Then we discovered how
to avenge this injustice
and obliterate those
who condemned us
to this wretchedness.
Now the moment is at hand.
No one is going to stop me.
Why are you so desperate
to save this girl?
The Shinenju is a mass
of collective memories,
nothing more.
The worthless remains of
what used to be alive.
‐No she’s not.
You’re wrong.
Senna is alive.
And she’s here.
She was confused and
afraid, looking for help.
She’s done nothing wrong,
but you want to destroy her.
I made a promise
that I’d protect her,
and I swore it on my soul.
[shout]
‐[whimper]
‐That’s it.
I understand now.
All of you are just‐‐ Ichigo.
‐We pass out of critical
range in 20 minutes.
‐Why haven’t they contacted us?
What’s going on?
‐There’s no time.
We must fire.
‐Sensei, please.
‐Commence firing the cannon.
‐They fired the cannon.
‐It won’t be long before the
entire dimension collapses.
‐What the hell?
‐My Zanpakuto’s
tougher than you think.
But underestimating my power is
going to be your last mistake.
‐You can’t escape.
‐I’m not planning
on running away.
‐You’ll wish you had.
‐Dance, Sode no Shirayuki!
‐Nice try.
‐Some no mai, Tsukishiro!
What?
‐I told you.
You can’t escape.
‐Byakuya.
‐As you pass into
the next life, feel
honored that you
perished by my Bankai.
Scatter, Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
‐[shouting]
‐Byakuya.
‐Come, Rukia.
‐Senna!
Time for you to die.
‐Come on.
[shouting]
‐You’re awfully quiet for once.
Hey, what’s the matter?
Cat got your tongue?
‐Shut your big fat mouth.
‐They’re coming back.
‐They’ve successfully
retrieved the Shinenju.
The Valley of Screams
is disintegrating.
‐Welcome home.
‐Rukia.
‐You actually did it, Ichigo.
‐Yeah.
‐Job well done.
You’re all to be congratulated.
‐You’re all right.
We were so worried.
‐Rukia.
Renji.
Thank you.
‐You idiot.
It’s not like we did it for you.
‐Yeah, I didn’t think the
big moocher had it in him.
‐What are you talking about?
‐Don’t worry, we’ll feed you.
‐Senna, I forgot.
I still have your ribbon.
‐Ichigo.
‐What’s going on?
Why is the alarm
continuing to sound?
‐It’s no good.
The dimension passed
beyond the critical zone.
Gravity is pulling the World of
the Living and the Soul Society
together on a collision course.
‐What’s this all about?
‐It isn’t stopping.
‐Then what’s going to happen?
‐This isn’t good.
‐Senna.
Why is this happening?
‐This is bad.
‐Dammit.
Isn’t there anything we can do?
‐Ichigo.
I’m scared.
‐Senna.
‐I won’t do it.
I just can’t.
I can’t allow it.
Not when this is such
a wonderful world
with so many beautiful
people living in it.
Not where you live, Ichigo.
I can’t let that happen.
It’s OK.
The Blanks are still near me,
and I’m not afraid of them now.
If I return their memories to
them, then they’ll be at peace.
And the barrier between the two
worlds will be strong again.
‐But Senna.
‐If the world were destroyed,
then there would be no Ichigo.
I can’t imagine a
world without you.
‐Stop!
You can’t do this.
‐No, Ichigo, I would never
allow you to die in front of me.
‐No, Senna.
Senna!
‐Confirming countless
spiritual explosions
in the Dangai Precipice World.
The Soul Society and
the World of the Living
are both moving towards their
previous stable positions.
The collision has been averted.
‐Ichigo, I have a favor to ask.
I want you to take me back
and check my family grave.
Remember yesterday when
I told you it was here,
I was alive once, and
I lived in this town.
I know it.
‐Yeah.
‐I don’t remember everything.
But I did have a family.
I’m certain of it.
I was in this world,
and I was alive.
So there has to be
a name on the grave.
‐You know, it was
right around here.
‐It was just down this
row, fourth from the end.
Is there a name?
My vision is blurred, and
I can’t see very well.
Is it there?
‐It’s there.
Clear as day.
You used to live in this
town, and you had a family.
‐I’m so happy.
I feel warm.
Ichigo.
Will we ever meet again?
‐What you talking about?
Of course, we will.
‐The energy from the Blanks
is slowly dissipating.
Soon it will all be gone.
Once that happens,
everything about Senna
will fade from our memories.
She was never alive
in our lifetime,
so you can’t remember
someone who didn’t exist.
‐I know she’ll be gone
soon, but right now, I
can still hear her voice.
[theme music]