Hey...
They say it's five centimeters per second.
Huh? What is?
The speed cherry blossom petals
fall is five centimeters per second.
Really...
You know a lot of stuff like that, Akari.
You know, they look just like snowflakes...
I guess...
Hey!
Wait up!
Akari!
Takaki.
I hope that we can see the cherry
blossoms together next spring.
Dear Takaki Tono...
I'm sorry that I haven't written for so long.
Though summers are hot here too,
they're a lot milder than Tokyo's.
But when I think about it,
I liked the hot, humid summers of Tokyo too.
The melting-hot pavement,
and skyscrapers in the distant, shimmering in the heat,
and the freezing air-conditioning
in department stores and on subways.
The last time we were together was
at our elementary school graduation.
It's been half a year since then.
Do you still remember me?
Dear Takaki...
Thank you for writing me back. It made me so happy.
It's already well into autumn and
the leaves are turning beautiful colors.
The day before yesterday, I pulled out
a sweater for the first time this year.
Tono?
Hi.
What's that? A love letter?
No, it's not.
Sorry for having asked you to do all that.
Oh, It's no problem.
Thank you.
Hey, are you really transferring to another school?
Yeah, at the end of the school year.
Where?
To Kagoshima. Because of my parents.
Really? We'll miss you...
Lately, I've been getting up
early because of school activities.
So, I'm writing this letter on the train.
I had my hair cut the other day.
It's so short that my ears even show.
You probably wouldn't even recognize me.
I'm home.
Hi, Mom.
I bet you'll change little by little over time too.
Dear Takaki...
Are you doing all right even with all this cold weather?
Here, it's already snowed a few times.
Every time it does, I have to really
bundle myself up when I go to school.
I'm sure it hasn't snowed in Tokyo yet, has it?
I'm aways checking Tokyo's weather too,
even though I don't live there anymore.
I sure wish it would rain.
When being any easier indoors.
Hey, have either of you guys ever been to Tochigi?
Where?
Tochigi.
Nope.
So you know how to get there?
I don't know... On the bullet train maybe?
A long way...
Freshman!
Coming!
Last three times!
Fight! Go! Fight! Go! Fight! Go!
I was really surprised when I heard
that you'll be transferring schools.
We both got used to transferring
schools when we were little.
But still, Kagoshima...
that's kind of far away, isn't it?
It's no longer a distance where I can just
jump on a train and see you whenever I want...
It does make me feel...
Well... kind of sad.
I just hope that you'll be fine.
Dear Takaki...
I'm so happy we'll see each other on March 4th.
It'll have been a year since we last met.
For some reason, I feel kind of nervous.
There's a big cherry tree by my house.
When the spring comes, the petals
will fall at five centimeters per second.
How I wish the spring could
come along with you on that day...
Do you wanna stop by somewhere on the way back?
Might as well, since it's raining and all...
They said it's going to turn to
snow tonight on The weather report.
Really? I thought it felt cold.
And we're already in March...
I hope we don't get colds.
Hey, we should go have something hot to drink.
Yeah, let's do that.
Tono.
Let's get to practice.
Oh yeah, practice...
Actually, I can't make it today.
Getting ready to move?
Yeah. Sorry.
It's so nice of you, coming all the way to my station...
It's a long trip, so be sure to take care of yourself.
I'll be waiting for you at 7:00 that
night in the station's waiting room.
That afternoon, on the day I was to meet Akari...
It started to snow.
Hey, Takaki. It's that cat, Chobi.
He's the one that's always here, isn't he?
But it looks like he's alone today.
Where's Mimi, Kiddy?
Aren't you kind of sad being all alone?
How do you like the book?
I like it. Last night I read four
billion years' worth of evolution.
Which part?
Where they talk about the Anomalooaris.
The Cambrian Age!
I really love the Halluoigenias.
They look like this.
Yeah, something like that...
So what's your favorite?
The Opabinia, I guess...
He mean the one with five eyes?
As I look back, I think Akari
and I were very alike somehow.
One year after I'd transferred to the school in Tokyo,
Akari transferred there, too, and was in my class.
We were both kind of small for our age,
and we both had really bad allergies, so
we preferred the library to the playground.
So, naturally, we got close to each other.
It caused our classmates to tease us.
But it didn't matter much to us
because of the friendship we had.
Aw, It's so cute.
For some reason, I just assumed that
we'd be going to the same junior high...
and that we'd be always together.
Shinjuku, Shinjuku. This is the terminal station.
For passengers getting off, please change
to the kyo-O subway for all J.R. lines.
It was the first time I had
been to Shinjuku Station alone.
And it would be the first time I had
been to any of those places on my route.
My heart was pounding.
I was going to meet Akari.
So tell me, how did it go with that guy?
Who?
The one from Nishi Sapporo.
Him? Don't you think he's a dork?
We'll soon be arriving at Musashi Urawa station.
Musashi Urawa station.
There wll be a 4-minute stop
as we wait for a "Rapid" line.
Passengers heading to Yonohon Town and
Omiya, please change to the express line.
Um... This is Akari Shinohara.
May I speak to Takaki please?
It's Akari.
Transferring schools?
What about Nishi Junior High?
After all that work to get a exam it.
They said they'd do the paperwork
to get me into a school in Tochigi.
I'm sorry.
No... There's nothing for you to apologize for...
I told them I wanted to stay with
my aunt in Katsushika, and commute.
But they objected, saying I'd
have to wait until I'm older...
All right.
Don't tell me any more!
That's enough.
Sorry...
I held the receiver so tight against my ear,
it was as though I could feel
Akari's pain directly through the phone.
But there was nothing I could do.
That was tasted good!
Yeah. thanks a lot, good bye!
See you later.
The terminal station, where I switched
trains, was filled with commuters heading home.
Everyone's shoes were soaked with snow and water.
The air was chilly and full of that
certain smell a city has on a snowy day.
This is an announcement for all passengers.
Utsunomiya lines bound for Oyama and Utsunomiya
wll arrive 8 minutes behind schedule due to heavy snow.
We apologize for any inconvenience.
Until that moment, it never even crossed my mind
that the train might be delayed.
Suddenly I became really worried.
Due to snow, this train is
running 10 minutes behind schedule.
Please accept our apologies for any inconvenience.
A short while after passing Omiya Station,
the buildings dotting the
scenery became few and far between
in what seemed like the blink of an eye.
The next stop is Kuki.
We apologize for having arrived far behind schedule.
Those passengers changing to the Tobuiseisaki line
please proceed to line 5.
This train wll stop for 10 minutes at this
station due to the late arrival of a connecting train.
We apologize for the delay,
and appreciate your understanding.
Sorry, sir...
This train wll stop for 10 minutes at this
station due to the late arrival of a connecting train.
We apologize for the delay, and
appreciate your understanding...
This is Nogi.
We would like to express our apologies as
this train wll temporarily stop at this station,
due to the late arrival of a connecting train.
The stations seemed unbelievably far apart.
And each time the train stopped at a station,
Seemed like an eternity.
The unfamiliar snow-covered wilderness outside the window,
the slow passage of time,
and hunger...
All of these added to my feeling of uneasiness.
I'm already late to meet her.
I'm sure she's starting to worry...
On that day...
the day I got that call...
Akari must have been much more upset than even I was.
And I wasn't able to comfort her...
I felt so ashamed of myself.
Well... I guess today we say good-bye...
I received the first letter from her half a year later.
During the summer of my first year in junior high.
I knew her letter by heart.
Over the two weeks before the day we were to meet,
I wrote a letter to give to Akari.
There were just so many things that I wanted to tell her.
So many things I wanted to ask her.
We apologize for the delay. The
train wll soon depart for Utsunomiya.
This is Oyama.
Passengers on the bullet train
bound for Tohoku change here.
Those passengers bound for
Morioka on the Tohoku Bullet train
please proceed to line 1.
Passengers bound for Tokyo please proceed to line 5.
The passengers taking the Mito line...
The followng is an announcement for all passengers.
Trains running on the Ryomo lines are running
significantly behind schedule due to heavy snow.
We apologize forthis delay. And ask that you
wait patiently for the arrival of the trains.
All I could do...
...was to keep heading for the
station where Akari was waiting for me.
Line 8, from Ashikaga / Maebashi and
bound for Takasaki, is now arriving.
Please remain inside the white
lines when exiting the train.
This announcement is for all passengers.
Due to heavy snowfall, service forthis train
wll be delayed for the sake of route rescheduling.
We apologize forthis delay, but at present are
not at liberty to say when service wll resume.
I repeat:
Due to heavy snowfall, service for this train
wll be delayed for the sake of route rescheduling.
We apologize forthis delay, but at present are
not at liberty to say when service wll resume.
Dear Takaki, how are you?
Lately I've been getting up early
because I'm busy with school activities.
When I read her letters, I always envisioned her alone.
In the end, the train spent around two
hours, motionless, in the middle of nowhere.
Every minute seemed like an eternity.
Time felt heavy with malice, as it slowly crept by.
All I could do was grit my teeth
and try to hold back my tears.
Akari.
Please...
Don't wait for me... If you'd just go back home...
Line 3, from Ashikaga / Maebashi and
bound for Takasaki, is now arriving.
Due to heavy snowfall, service
forthis train wll be temporarily delayed.
Akari.
This is good...
Really? It's just regular roasted tea.
Roasted tea? I've never had it before.
What?! I'm sure you have.
You think?
Of course!
I made this for you.
So, I can't promise it's any good.
Have some if you want.
Thank you.
I haven't eaten in hours.
So... How is it?
I've never had anything so delicious before.
You're exaggerating!
I'm serious!
It's just because you're hungry.
You think?
I'm sure it is.
I'll have some, too.
You're going to move soon, right?
Yeah, next week.
Kagoshima, huh...
It's so far away.
Yeah...
But it turned out that Tochigi is quite a ways away, too!
It is. I guess you won't be able to go home now!
We're gonna have to close up kids,
I'm sorry there are no more trains.
Okay.
Take care, it's snowing heavily out there.
Thank you.
Can you see it? That tree?
The one you wrote about in your letter?
Yes, the cherry tree.
Hey...
They look like snowflakes.
You are right, they do.
At that moment...
I felt like I understood things like the
existence of eternity, the heart and the soul.
I felt as though we had shared
all the experiences of my 13 years.
And the next moment...
I became unbearably sad.
Sad because I didn't know what
to do with her warmth against me
or what to do with that soul, or
how long I should hold onto them.
I also came to the clear realization
that we would not be able to remain together.
The overwhelming weight of our lives to
come and the uncertainty of time hung over us.
But soon, all my fears began to melt away,
leaving only Akari's soft lips on mine.
That night, we stayed in a tiny
shack by the corner of a field.
Wrapped up in an old blanket, we talked all night...
Until finally, we fell asleep.
The next morning, when the train
is started, I got ready leave.
And there, Akari and I said good-bye.
I...
Takaki...
Takaki, I think you'll be...
You will be okay! I know you will be!
Thank you for that.
Take care of yourself! Akari
I'll write to you. I'll call!
I didn't even mention the letter I lost.
Because after we'd kissed...
...it seemed like the whole world had completely changed.
I wanted so badly to be able to protect her.
That was all I could think about,
as I gazed absently out the window.
Kanae, you going after class too?
Yeah, how about you, Sis?
Sure. But make sure you do your homework too. Okay?
I will.
Here goes...
Good morning, Kanae.
Hello, Tono. You're early again.
You too, Sumida.
Did you go to the beach?
Sure did.
You're practicing hard.
Well, not really...
See you later, Tono.
Later.
Are we ready? It's about time to make your decisions.
I need all of you to get this to me by Monday.
Talk it over with your parents.
It sounds like Sasaki's going to a university in Tokyo.
I'll probably have to go to
some junior college in Kumamoto.
And you, Kanae?
Well...
So, will you get a job?
Ummm...
You're not thinking about anything, are you?
Nothing except Takaki Tono.
I bet he has a girl back in Tokyo.
Cut it out!
Still having a rough time?
I don't know what's wrong...
You shouldn't worry yourself so much.
You'll catch a right way again.
You're so easygoing, you know that.
So, what's the big rush?
Keep this up, I'll graduate without saying anything...
Okay, thanks a lot. See you later.
I can give you a ride.
That's all right. I'll take my scooter.
Sumida, you heading home now?
Uh... yeah. You too, Tono?
Uh-huh.
Want to head back together?
If I was a dog, my tail would wagging so hard.
My happiness would have been obvious.
I heaved the sigh of relief, thinking
it was a good thing I wasn't a dog...
And I was amazed with how stupid a thought that was...
even for me.
Yet...
The ride back home with Tono made me so happy.
Right from the beginning, Tono
seemed somehow different from others.
I'm Takaki Tono.
I'm used to transferring schools because of my
Dad's job, but I'm not used to this island yet.
It's nice to meet you all.
That very day, when I was in
8th grade, I fell in love with him.
I studied hard because I wanted to
go to the same high school as him...
And somehow, I managed to pass
my school's entrance exams...
The more I see Tono, the more I love him.
It's been scary... Every day's been painful.
But... Every time I see him, I'm happy.
And there was nothing I could do about it.
Tono, same thing again?
It's so good!
You really think about things, I mean
there's always so much thought involved.
Yeah, I guess.
Okay, I'll be outside.
Okay...
I'll have this.
That'll be 90 yen.
Here.
Thank you very much.
There you are. What did you buy?
Well, at first I couldn't decide, but...
Sometimes I see Tono writing e-mails to somebody.
I can't help wishing that he was writing to me...
Every time I see it.
Hey, Cub! I'm home!
Come here, Cub! I'm back now!
The followng is a Town Hall announcement:
The Kanae Sumida of class 3-1 police
report to Mr. Ito in the counseling room.
Kanae Sumida of class 3-1.
Please report to Mr. Ito in the counseling room.
Hey Tono, that's your girl.
She's not my girlfriend.
We're at year-end, and you're
the only one not to turn this in.
I'm sorry.
Hey, I really don't want to say it like this...
But, this is not something to
get yourself so worked up over.
Has your sister said anything to you about?
No...
If you can't make up your mind, why not
try a junior college in the prefecture?
Because...
This doesn't have anything to do with my sister...
I mean...
whether it's this surting, which I
nagged my sister to let me start, or him,
the most important person in the entire world to me...
I'm not getting anywhere with either...
Thanks again. Good night to you.
Thanks. Have a nice night. See you later.
When I get near Tono I get this
tight sensation deep in my chest.
Tono.
Sumida, What's up? How did you know I was here?
I saw your scooter, so I stopped by. Is that okay?
Yeah. I'm glad you came by.
I mean, since we couldn't meet in
the parking lot like we usually do.
Yeah!
He's so nice...
Sometimes it makes me want to cry.
Hey Tono. Are you going to test to get into college?
Yeah, a college in Tokyo.
Tokyo... Really...
I kind of thought so...
Why's that?
You just kinda seem like you want to
go somewhere far away. For some reason...
How about you, Sumida?
I don't even know what I'll do tomorrow.
Maybe nobody does.
Really?! Even you?
Naturally.
But you seem to know exactly what you are doing.
That's weird because I don't
really. I'm lost all the time.
I just do what I can. That's all I can do.
Really?
Yeah, you're right.
Making a plane?
Yes.
That's amazing.
Told at five km per hour.
To the South Tanega launch facility.
Huh.
There's gonna be a launch this year, isn't there?
Yeah.
They say it's going to go all the
way to center of the solar system...
It'll take years...
I want you to give Kanae advice
on her future. She's so unfocused.
She'll be all right. She's not a kid anymore.
You know I was just like her at her age.
Listen Cub, Tono doesn't know where he's going either.
He's just like me, that Tono.
It must really be...
...a lonelier journey than anyone could imagine.
Cutting through absolute darkness...
...encountering nothing except
the occasional stray hydrogen atom.
Flying blindly into the abyss, believing there in
lie the answers to the mysteries of the universe.
And us...
To that end, how far should we go?
And how far can we go?
I wonder when I got in the habit
of writing messages to nobody?
Kanae, have you figured out what
you're going to do after your graduation?
Not yet. But it's fine...
I've made a decision.
I'll just start by doing each and every thing that I can!
I'm off!
After that day, several typhoons have passed the island.
And each time they did, it became cooler.
The wind that blew across the
sugarcane fields got crisper.
The sky looked a little bigger.
And the outlines of the clouds grew softer.
The kids in my grade who rode
scooters started wearing their jackets.
Then, on a mid-October day
tinged with the remains of summer,
I rode a wave for the first time in six months.
Tonight's forecast is clear wth
maximum wnd speeds of 8 meters per second.
I heard Yamada told Sasaki that he likes her.
That is expected.
Huh? Kanae, you sure seem happy today.
Did something happen with Tono?
No way?!
All right, class.
What is important is this formula? It's...
Today, I'm going to tell Tono how I feel about him.
If I don't tell him today, after
riding that wave... I'll never be able to.
Sumida.
Hello, Tono.
Heading home now?
Yeah.
Really...
Well... let's head home together.
Oh! You decided already?
Yeah.
What is it?
Don't be so...
So what?
Sorry...
It's nothing.
Something wrong?
Yeah, that's strange...
No good?
No...
I wonder if the spark plug's dead...
Was this a hand-me-down?
Yeah, from my big sister.
Was it cutting out on you when you'd accelerate?
It might have been...
Well, let's leave them both here. We can
have somebody can pick them up later for us.
We can walk it.
I can walk by myself, Tono. You just head on home.
I've only got a little ways left to go.
Besides, I kind of feel like walking.
Tono.
Please...
What's wrong?
Sorry, it's nothing.
I'm sorry...
Sumida...
I'm begging you... please...
...don't be so nice to me.
Desperately, reaching recklessly towards the sky...
Launching that massive object, in search of something
almost overwhelmingly far off in the distance...
I began to understand why Tono
seemed different from the others.
At the same time, I came to a very clear
realization that Tono was never looking at me.
So that day, I didn't say anything to Tono.
Tono is certainly nice...
Very nice indeed...
But...
Tono's always looking past me...
At something far beyond.
I guess my wishes to be with Tono will never come true.
But I still...
But I still won't be able to stop loving him.
Not today, not tomorrow, not ever.
I fell asleep that night crying,
the only thoughts in my head being of Tono...
I felt it strongly...
that if I'd turned around at that
moment, she'd have turned to look at me too.
The last Chuo line train bound for Tokyo is now arriving.
I wish you'd stay for the New Year's holiday...
I know, but I have a lot of preparations.
I suppose so.
Make sure you cook something nice for him.
I will.
Call us anytime you need to, Akari.
Okay?
I'll be fine.
I'll see you again at the wedding next month.
Don't worry so much.
You'd better head home. It's cold.
Last night I dreamt about the past.
When we were both still children.
I guess it's because of the old letter I found yesterday.
Mizuno.
Yes?
The meeting. Let's go.
Coming.
In just living my life, it's as
though sadness piles up all around me.
It's on my bed, dried in the sun...
the toothbrush in my bathroom...
In the memory of my cell-phone...
"I still love you."
That's what the girl I'd been with
for three years said in that e-mail.
She wrote, "We must have exchanged e-mails 1000 times.
But I doubt our hearts got
closer by more than a centimeter."
For the past few years, I've wanted to move on...
To grasp onto something beyond my reach...
What that is, I don't even know...
All I've been able to do is go on working,
not knowing where these obsessive thoughts come from...
Then one day I realized that my heart was
withering, and in it there was nothing but pain.
Then one morning...
...I realized that my beliefs, that I once
held so passionately, had completely disappeared.
That was it, I couldn't take any more.
So I quit my job.
Yesterday I had a dream.
A dream of long ago.
In the dream, we were still 13 years old.
And we were standing in a field covered with snow...
where in the dim light from distant houses,
our footsteps were all that could
be seen in the new-fallen snow.
And because of that, we both
believed without any doubt that.
Someday, together we'd watch
the cherry blossoms fall again...
...Again.