[JOE] In the beginning
was the Voice,
and the Voice was Him.
And man would listen to
His Voice in great awe.
But through vanity,
pride, deceit, and greed,
man hoarded the
riches of the earth,
raising a great many towers
whose tops reached unto heaven.
As man's arrogance scattered
its people among ravaged lands,
so was His Voice ignored.
Yet, He gave man
a chance to atone.
[yelling and screaming]
[JOE] And flame and smoke
and a great roar of lions
fell upon the earth.
[scattered yells]
[JOE] Though pay heed,
listeners to His Voice.
For some ordeals
waged in His honor
may not force man
to hear as thou.
[ANCHORWOMAN] On February 26,
at about 3:30 PM...
[JOE] May the
devout bring justice
to all people of the earth,
and let mankind start anew.
May His Voice free us from sin
and bless us with glory, honor,
and prosperity unending.
[ANCHORWOMAN] At least
six buildings in total
have now collapsed
throughout the area,
with surrounding buildings
sustaining major damage.
Fires and debris leave the
area in a state of confusion,
severely impeding rescue
efforts. At this time,
we can only confirm that the
situation is far from contained.
While it is too
early to determine
an exact body count,
current estimates put
the number of casualties
at least ten thousand.
Chinese authorities have
declared the disaster
a terrorist act, and martial
law is currently in effect
throughout Shanghai,
as no civilians are permitted
to enter or exit the region.
Today's tragedy appears
related to the series
of suicide bombings that began
in America on January 16th
with synchronized attacks
on Chicago's Willis Tower
and Seattle's Columbia Center.
The identity of those behind
the series of attacks...
[JOE] Well planned. Must've been
in the works for some time.
[ANCHORWOMAN]
...as none have come forward
to claim responsibility...
They've beaten me to it.
[ANCHORWOMAN] As for the
collateral damage incurred
from the Financial Center's
collapse, experts say that...
[JOE] Hey, Mom?
I'll be out late tonight.
What? No, It's not a date
or anything like that...
[WAITRESS]
Hello there.
[GREAT BRITAIN]
Hello, Jet.
So now it's Shanghai, then.
Yeah, I've heard.
Been a while.
Well, 9/11 was, what?
'Bout twelve years ago?
How you holding up?
Haven't slacked
with my constant,
pain-in-the-ass maintenance,
so not so bad.
[GREAT BRITAIN] Well, you're
sounding a little testy.
Anything you want
to talk about?
Just take your pick.
The news spreads nothing
but paranoia lately.
The President's baffled.
And now we've gotta
come running just
'cause Gilmore says so?
I suppose.
How can we blow off the guy
who made us what we are?
Whenever there's trouble we
obey him, for the greater good.
Zero-Zero Cyborgs don't
get to call their own shots.
[JET] G.B., do you think
America was involved in this?
[GREAT BRITAIN] Actually,
I've got Israeli lobbyists
saying my boys in
Parliment set it all up,
as a great big gift to
our defense contractors.
Well, that's today's gossip.
So, what makes you ask?
You're not having a
"crisis of confidence"
in your lot's brand
of justice, are you?
Hm. Forget it.
If these bombings keep up,
everyone will get their turn
at the blame game. Then
things'll really go to hell.
And when they do, we'll all
have forgetten the times
when nations could
keep each other in check.
It's really coming down.
Sorry we're late.
It's been a slow night.
Nothing to report.
[TOMOE]
Joe, over here!
[TOMOE pants]
What do you know?
I thought I was the one
always dragging you out.
I would stand out
too much coming alone.
Huh?
I love coffee.
[TOMOE] You must be able to see
Tokyo Tower from your place!
[JOE]
Not since Tower D went up.
Huh?
Hey, how come you
ditched school today?
We're on break.
What's the point of going?
[TOMOE] Joe, I don't
think I've seen you talk
with anyone else at school.
Maybe we could try to hang
out with some of my friends?
You act like you don't
want to be noticed, ever.
Ah--! Why do you say that?
Just been noticing.
Ah... I never knew...
You've been keeping
an eye on me, huh?
Found you, 009.
This probably sounds
like nonsense to you,
but I feel like I've been
stuck in high school forever,
and it just won't end.
And it also feels like I've been
under observation all the while.
Yeah, I know I felt that way
during my entrance exams.
[JOE sighs]
This is different...
Really different...
[JOE sighs]
Also, how long have we been
going out now, anyway?
I'm not even sure how long it is
you've been putting up with me.
And if I honestly don't know
something that important,
then I guess I must have
already lost my mind
a really long time ago.
It's fine. Don't worry, Joe.
C'mere. You're just tired.
[JOE] I still have to
answer to His Voice.
And deliver justice.
[GREAT BRITAIN]
Jet, I need to ask you this
strictly off the record.
Have you heard of something
called "His Voice"?
Whose voice do you mean?
Not one government agency
has been able to find
even a single connection between
any of the suicide bombers
in their investigations.
But there's been this one
phrase I've kept running into
ever since I began looking into
this mess here in the U.S.
[JET] And that
would be "His Voice"?
Right. Before the
two U.K. bombings,
and the ones in
France and Hong Kong,
each of these people
made some kind of noise
about obeying "His Voice"
before blowing themselves up.
They all said they wanted to
help mankind "start anew."
Help us "start anew"?
So... Whose voice is it?
Not a clue. A leader of some
kind of fundamentalist sect?
A syndicate boss backed
by Neocons? Hell, maybe it's
some charmismatic sociopath
building up a crazy new cult.
But considering we've
got no other connection
between any of the previous
thirty-three bombers,
this could be just the break
we've been looking for.
I'll be handing this
to the appropriate
intelligence agencies.
Just thought you should know.
Probably safest to keep
it to yourself for now.
Cheers, Jet. Less work
talk next time, hm?
G.B., you're really
meeting up in Istanbul?
[GREAT BRITAIN] Well,
I can't exactly come and go
as I please, now, can I?
I'll make proper arrangements
with SIS before I pop off.
I'm sure.
So, how's he been?
Remember, Jet: Butting in only
makes it worse with you two.
Now what? He's out in public.
[FRANCOISE]
Lure him up to the roof.
Then do what you have to do.
And don't hold back.
Incoming cruise missile?!
What's wrong? Francoise?!
[indistinct talking
and screaming]
[MAN IN BACKGROUND]
What's that?
[TOMOE]
What?
A bomb?!
[FRANCOISE gasps]
[GERONIMO JR.] What's going on?
Is it a suicide bomber?
[FRANCOISE] No, this looks
like something else.
Just get to 009
and wake him up!
I'm on it.
[JOE gasps]
[GERONIMO JR. grunts]
[JOE groans]
[JOE grunts]
[JOE pants]
[JOE shudders]
[GERONIMO JR. grunts]
[GERONIMO JR. roars]
[FRANCOISE gasps]
[GERONIMO JR. grunts]
[JOE pants]
What is this?!
Are you the one
doing all this?!
[GERONIMO JR. grunts]
[JOE grunts]
[GERONIMO JR. yells]
[JOE groans]
[GERONIMO JR. roars]
[JOE gasps]
[GERONIMO JR.
grunts repeatedly]
[GERONIMO JR. grunts]
[JOE]
Again?! What's going on?
[JOE pants]
[GERONIMO JR. growls]
[JOE]
Francoise!
Activate Acceleration!
[JOE pants]
[JOE]
What were you thinking?!
Hi, Joe. Welcome back.
If you're here, then it means
we're all needed again.
That's it, it's it?
Yes. It is. Skyscrapers are
being attacked across the world,
and no one knows
who's behind it.
It's time for Dr. Gilmore
to summon us again.
So you're back?
Mm. Been a while, Geronimo.
Right.
Was this another
suicide bombing?
I don't know. But the
missiles were launched
from an American vessel.
[FRANCOISE gasps]
[JOE] Their backup
generator finally kicked in.
[FRANCOISE gasps]
You seem to know
that building.
[JOE]
Mm.
Pyunma, it sounds
like Jet doesn't know
a thing about His Voice.
And if Jet's not in the loop,
then His Voice is something
far more dangerous than
an American conspiracy,
just like like you thought.
Hm. I guess it isn't
just the President
who doesn't know what
the hell's going on.
[AGENT grunts]
[AGENT groans]
[cracking noise]
[GREAT BRITAIN]
Hazra... Hm.
Bloody NSA... Hm?
Cyborgs were supposed to fight
for justice, weren't they?
[GREAT BRITAIN gasps]
[phone rings]
[phone chime]
[JET]
It's me.
Fired them into Tokyo?!
He said that?
"His Voice"?
[JET pants]
Chang Changku here.
Harbor infiltrated!
Requesting further
intructions, Ivan.
[IVAN] Understood.
I'm surprised you've accepted
the Doctor's mission
so readily, 006.
[CHANG]
Mm?
[IVAN] It's unfortunate
that the legal dispute
between you two
is still ongoing.
Was it necessary
to trademark
the name "Chang Changku" for
your restaurant franchise?
Hey, let's not dwell,
all right? Ah!
The whole restaurant thing
might have rubbed Gilmore
the wrong way, but even us
cyborgs have got to eat.
And fighting for justice
just does not pay the bills.
As long as the Gilmore
Foundation gets
a fat donation in my name
each year, all's fair!
[CHANG grunts]
So, how's this shipping company
connected to the bombings?
Doesn't look like they're moving
anything suspicious to me.
[IVAN] You've heard about
the Tokyo bombing, correct?
Uh-huh. So we've really got
American cruise missiles
in the middle
of all this now?
[IVAN] Yes. That prompted
me to reinvestigate
the initial attacks
in America.
[CHANG]
Oh?
[IVAN] And it appears that
this shipping company, SMO,
had illegally sold off
the collapsed buildings'
wreckage into China.
[CHANG]
Wreckage from the attacks
would be pretty important
evidence, wouldn't it?
[IVAN] Definitely.
And a civilian company
sending evidence abroad, before
any proper examination, no less,
is very suspicious.
[CHANG]
Indeed it is.
Hwah!
[CHANG grunts]
[CHANG] If Ivan's right
about this place,
I should turn up some missile
fragments somewhere...
[CHANG yells]
[CHANG grunts]
[CHANG pants]
[CHANG yelps]
[CHANG]
Hraaah!
[CHANG] Now, put your
hands behind your heads!
[CHANG gasps]
[CHANG yells]
[CHANG grunts]
[CHANG] So this is
how they operate?
Blowing yourself up's even more
pathetic than using a missile!
[CHANG coughs]
[CHANG] God-fearing men
don't work this way!
Despicable!
[CHANG growls]
Again, I lived,
while you only waited.
[HEINRICH] Wouldn't have
thought you'd settle
into archeology, Pyunma.
Well, the plan was for adventure
and glory. But as you can see,
my schedule was wide open
when Dr. Gilmore called.
Although... if my
investigations in Africa
really can help us out here,
it's all been worth it.
[HEINRICH]
Damn right.
Who needs glory, huh?
I'm surprised you were
the first one to get here.
So the GSG gives you
that much leeway?
My whole body's made
of one-off parts.
Some think I'm not even worth
the trouble to maintain. So...
I'm not much more
than a Cold War relic.
They'll still dust me off
to give demonstrations
for the engineers.
But it's just a matter of time
before they ship me
off to a museum.
[various indistinct murmurs
among the crowd]
Heh. It'll take us all
night to reach the lab.
Hey, stop the jeep!
[HEINRICH]
What's wrong?
Pyunma!
[PYUNMA pants]
[PYUNMA gasps]
Hey. Did a young girl
come through here?
[lively chatter]
[PYUNMA gasps]
That's it.
What they meant
by "His Voice."
What in the hell...?
[DR. GILMORE chuckles]
[DR. GILMORE] It's good
to have you back, Joe.
[IVAN]
It's nice to see you, 009.
Yeah, 001. You too.
It's been twenty-seven years.
And of course you
haven't changed one bit,
now, have you, Joe?
Leading a normal life during
peace time could prove
complicated with a body
like yours that doesn't age.
That's why I've reset
your mind every three years
and locked away
your memories of us.
I felt this would afford
you the stability needed
to act as leader of
the Zero-Zero Cyborgs
should ever the need arise.
Looking back,
I believe my choice
has burdened you,
nonetheless.
What's important is,
you're here now.
Yeah. Although I have to say,
repeating high school
over and over had gotten
more than a bit stifling.
You remembered it all?
The memories from each reset
seemed to linger, somehow.
And forcing you back here
cannot have helped matters.
It's OK. I'm feeling
a little mixed up,
but I can work through it.
And the others! How are they?
The rest all have formally
parted with the Foundation
and sought out work
in their home countries.
[DR. GILMORE sighs]
However, Heinrich and Pyunma
have just arrived in Istanbul,
and G.B. will join us once
he's received clearance
from Britain's Secret
Intelligence Service.
[IVAN] And we were
able to deploy 006
on a special
reconnaissance mission.
[JOE]
What about Jet?
[DR. GILMORE]
Hmm...
He couldn't still be--
[IVAN] 002 now works for
the National Security Agency
in the United States.
I doubt that he would
ever be granted permission
to team up with us again.
His absence is surely unrelated
to any bad blood
between you two.
Now, let me explain what
the NSA's involved with.
After the skyscraper bombings
originated in the United States,
a great deal of conspiracy
theories had arisen.
Obviously, several
of them suggest
the U.S. government's
possible involvement.
[IVAN] Have you heard
of Samuel Capital?
It's a private investment
fund based in America.
Though it acts on
behalf of its investors
in Israel's Ministry of Defense.
Samuel Capital has one goal:
to profit from the
military-industrial complex
by undermining world
peace and stability.
[Dr. GILMORE] The American
government seemed to have
supported this agenda,
believing it would ultimately
let the U.S. regain
global preeminence.
My theory is supported
by Congress ignoring
the illegal activities of
Samuel Capital's affiliates...
chief among them being
the Post-Humanity Project.
[IVAN] This includes the
development of cyborgs
called Lazarus that are
made from the corpses
of U.S. soldiers killed in Iraq,
as well as civilian casualties.
Cyborgs from corpses?!
[DR. GILMORE] Yes.
Chang's report will hopefully
tell us more on
this matter, but...
I suspect the initial
suicide bombings in America
were carried out by these
Lazarus-type cyborgs.
And by manufacturing
their own suicide bombers,
Samuel Capital is poised
to control a new war,
selling their exclusive
weapons and security services
all across the globe.
[IVAN] We believe the
United States government
and Samuel Capital's
subversive plan
is the true cause of the
international bombings,
and that the group charged with
facilitating this new means
of remote warfare is the same
one employing 002: the NSA.
[NAVYMAN] I'd failed
the U.S.-Japan-Korea
military simulation
fifteen days ago.
I haven't slept since then.
That was the first day
I heard His Voice.
In one moment, I was
addressing my C.O.
And in the next, I could
hear it speaking to me!
It was His Voice;
I had to answer!
[INTERROGATOR] Exactly whose
voice are you talking about?
[NAVYMAN shudders]
[INTERROGATOR]
Hm?
What's the matter?
[NAVYMAN
breathes heavily]
[INTERROGATOR]
Here, sit back down!
[INTERROGATOR yells]
[NAVYMAN chokes, gurgles]
[INTERROGATOR] This bastard
bit his tongue off!
[NAVAL OFFICER]
What's "His Voice"?
And just how much intel do
you people have on all this?
[FRANCOISE]
If Samuel Capital really is
some new kind
of Axis of Evil,
does this mean we'll be
going up against them?
It's a strong possibility.
But before we take any action,
we first must understand
precisely how Samuel Capital
was able to execute all 34
bombings across the globe.
And why the U.S. Navy
themselves fired a missile
into Japan,
an allied country.
These matters are
where we'll begin.
But know that in a
worst-case scenario,
we go up against the U.S.
military, as well as Jet.
[GERONIMO JR. sighs]
Doctor, I need to
ask you something
about your research
into these attacks...
Is it possible that all
of them were carried out
by those answering
His Voice?
[DR. GILMORE]
Hm?
Before the global attacks
even began, while I tried living
as a high-schooler, I heard
His Voice. That's why I was
planning to bomb Roppongi
Hills, and answer Him.
You had planned a
suicide bombing?
[FRANCOISE &amp;
GERONIMO JR. gasp]
[IVAN] 009, what do
you mean "His Voice"?
I guess it wasn't your voice
I heard, right, Doctor?
I was answering the voice
so I could join the fight
and help humanity
start over.
What are you saying?
Joe Shimamura,
is it really you?
[FRANCOISE &amp;
GERONIMO JR. gasp]
[JET] Even if the
Department of Defense
benefitted from
Samuel Capital's plan,
how could we let them
start a war on U.S. soil?
An unmanned war,
with an unseen enemy.
Did we know how far
things would escalate
after the U.S. bombings?
Regardless of what
we stand to gain,
how can we let Samuel Capital
go unchecked, when this is
growing into something we
may have no control over?
Hell, this situation with
"His Voice" is starting
to affect our
own soldiers now.
So, what is His Voice?
Another part of
Samuel Capital's plan?
They're capable of anything,
from wiretapping
to building weapons outta
corpses. Have they developed
some kind of brainwashing
technology, too? And...
...if they've got some
hidden agenda the NSA
doesn't know about,
we're as helpless as anyone.
[phone rings]
[NSA OFFICER]
Jet, we've got an emergency.
It's "His Voice" again.
[JET gasps]
Tell me where you heard
this "voice," Joe.
Sorry, It's hard for me
to pin down where or when.
I just know I was overcome
with this intense feeling
that answering His Voice
was without a doubt
the only way for me
to set things straight.
That's why I thought it
came from you, Doctor.
Hm, I see. So, are you saying
that the other bombers
were responding to
this voice as well?
Yes. If you look into
the Shanghai bombing,
you'll see it was in
the works long before
the initial attacks
on January 16th.
[IVAN] So you'd already
heard "His Voice" before?
Hm. A few months beforehand.
It's clear others must have
heard it and chosen
to take action as well.
Hm...  What is His Voice?
Francoise! Weren't you
the one watching Joe?!
Uh... Yes. But to watch
every moment seemed a...
It's possible some sort
of virus may have infected
the brainwave transmissions
used during his monitoring.
Francoise, review all
data transmissions to Joe
from the past three years.
I'll need to scan
your brain, Joe.
I ask for your cooperation.
Geronimo.
[PA] Doctor, we've
intercepted reports
stating the U.S. Air Force
lost contact with a B-2 bomber
three hours ago
over the Indian Ocean.
The B-2 was last spotted
over the Arabian Sea.
An F-38 fighter is now
in pursuit of the B-2.
The pilot of the F-38
appears to be Jet Link.
[JOE gasps]
I'm a little busy here, guys.
[muffled radio chatter]
Sorry.
[FRANCOISE]
I'm certain. It's Jet
who left the
combat airspace.
The B-2 is now crossing the Gulf
of Oman toward the Persian Gulf.
Is it headed for Iraq?
What the hell's happening?
The pilot in that B-2... I think
he also heard His Voice.
He's probably
targeting Dubai!
Are you saying this wasn't
planned by the U.S.?
[JOE] If Jet was
deployed to stop it,
I have to think it means
that the U.S. government
is being forced
to take action!
Doctor, have me teleported
to the pilot's airspace!
[FRANCOISE gasps]
I'll go, and find out
what's causing this!
No! You just admitted to us
that you had planned
a suicide bombing yourself!
I won't let you leave.
Francoise, put me through to the
U.S. Department of Defense, now.
Doctor, Joe is right. The U.S.
is being forced to act
against whatever's
causing this. We have help!
Ivan, we'll call Heinrich.
Teleport him to the scene.
We'll have him shoot down
the B-2 if necessary--
[DR. GILMORE gasps]
Stop it!
There's no way that
Heinrich can destroy a B-2.
Given that much
speed and altitude,
there's only two people
who can do this--
me, with my Accelerator,
and Jet, who can fly.
I have to find out
what His Voice is.
Doctor...
[IVAN]
Very well, 009.
[no audible dialogue]
[FRANCOISE gasps]
How could this happen?
Don't worry. I have faith
in Joe. Believe in him.
Joe! I can handle this!
Listen! I came for
the B-2's pilot!
I wanna find out if
he heard His Voice!
What did you say?!
You know about it?!
So you're saying that you
already know about His Voice?!
What's Gilmore
make of all this?
He'd never heard of it.
He knows nothing.
Dr. Gilmore thinks the NSA
and the whole U.S. government
are behind all these bombings!
Is Joe sending us this?!
[FRANCOISE]
Mm.
Well, then how do you know?!
Because I heard
His Voice myself.
I was actually planning
to bomb Roppongi.
[JET gasps]
My God, Joe...  Always on the
opposite corner, aren't you?
I thought we were
friends until that day.
But once we were
relieved from our duties,
it was the Japanese wonder
boy the Foundation kept.
A kid, put on global security?
And you're supposed to be
the leader during a crisis?
You're a joke!
Who protects peace and freedom?
America, that's who!
I know. But does that mean
it's the right thing
for the whole world?!
Well, the right thing for me...
...is to remove any
obstacles to my mission!
[JOE] If you're not being
manipulated to do this,
I'll back off. But if you are,
I'll answer His Voice
and help this pilot
carry out his mission.
[JET &amp; FRANCOISE gasp]
He's going to help the pilot?!
Joe, are you with us
or against us?!
[JET &amp; JOE grunt]
[JET gasps]
[JET grunts]
[JET pants]
[JOE gasps]
Look out!
[JOE grunts]
[JET gasps]
Joe!
[honking]
[indistinct screaming]
[MAN yells]
[JOE]
Can this...
Can this really be what
His Voice asked for?
The B-2... was carrying
an armed nuclear warhead?
Joe...
[IVAN] 003, can you detect any
brainwave transmission from Joe?
Too much interference.
[IVAN] News of this
tragedy will spread
across the world immediately.
[DR. GILMORE shudders]
Joe is dead now. What voice
could he have possibly heard?
It seems that now we have
no way of ever finding out.
[door opens]
[IVAN]
004! 006!
Sorry we're late.
What a terrible
situation this is, no?
And Pyunma?
He disappeared today.
But before that,
he'd actually found
something that's
related to this mess.
[IVAN]
What is that?
Is this... the fossil
of... an angel?
[MAN]
Yes, that's the situation.
We should assume
that recon satellites
have captured his
escape from Dubai.
As well as his landing here
at Andrews Air Force Base.
So concealing U.S. involvement
would be difficult.
Yes, sir.
[OFFICIAL] In that case,
we'll need to implement
a suitable cover story
as soon as possible.
Anyone have any ideas?
[MAN] Actually...
The photos I sent?
We leak them to media
outlets across the world.
[grunting]
I think I see where
you're headed with this.
[MAN] We've spent a fortune
planning to use this failsafe.
Now's the time, sir.
[OFFICIAL]
And what about His Voice?
[MAN] The B-2 pilot and
the soldiers who aided him
have all been
taken into custody.
Even as we speak
they're being questioned
on the matter,
and, of course,
a thorough investigation
is going to be conducted.
[GUARDS pant]
[GUARD]
Inform the commander.
[JET] The NSA was sympathetic
to your companies' goals.
And as such, they
gave you their direct
and indirect support
at every turn.
So I deserve some answers.
Several U.S. military personnel
were directly involved
in the last bombing.
And each one of them
claimed to have heard
something called "His Voice."
And if responsibility lies
right here at Samuel Capital,
then you should be greatly
concerned, Mr. Klein.
Now tell me what His Voice is!
[KLEIN groans]
[JET] The United States is
going to face accusations
from the whole world because
of this latest bombing!
We need to know what we're
dealing with here, and how
our own troops are getting
dragged into all of this!
[KLEIN]
Hm.
This state of affairs has
only ever proven itself
to be beneficial for us all.
Mankind is set on its path
to begin anew, whether we
choose to intervene or not.
What the hell
are you saying?
You take issue with this?
All we've ever done
is aided mankind by
answering His Voice.
[JET shudders]
[JOE sighs]
I have been unable to
make contact with G.B.
So, what? He's gotten
swept away by this "voice,"
just like Pyunma?
But what would the disappearance
of him have to do with G.B.'s?
Hmm...
Pyunma had discovered
that "angel fossil"
while researching Olduvai
Gorge down in Tanzania.
His notes say that,
as the skeleton was unearthed,
more and more
of his dig staff
claimed they'd started
hearing something.
Something they'd only
refer to as "His Voice."
[HEINRICH] They each
said the same thing...
"In the beginning
was the Voice.
And the Voice was Him.
And man would
listen to His Voice.
But through vanity,
pride, deceit, and greed,
man hoarded the
riches of the earth,
raising a great many towers
whose tops reached unto heaven.
As man's arrogance scattered
its people among ravaged lands,
so was His Voice ignored.
Yet, He gave man
a chance to atone.
And flame and smoke
and a great roar of lions
fell upon the earth.
And man's towers
were brought to dust."
If it's biblical,
I've not heard it.
[IVAN] That is because
there is no such passage
in any version of the Bible.
Pyunma knew that.
So he figured his staff
came across this "voice" thing
while they were all leafing
through some old apocrypha.
But, as soon as the bombings
started on January 16th,
Pyunma remembered.
Remembered every word they said.
It was like those
words described
all of the
skyscraper bombings
that suddenly began
happening everywhere.
And he knew that by
studying our origins,
he was studying how we think.
So, with that in mind, Pyunmna
hypothesized that his staffers
had a kind of "religious
experience" when they saw
that "angel" fossil,
an experience called
"His Voice." And Pyunma
wondered if, in a way,
they really had heard
a message from "God."
So then, what do
we make of that?
[HEINRICH] Hmm... Well,
this religious historian,
Mircea Eliade, wrote about
some "mystical solidarity"
between man and nature:
Hunting and farming had
taught our ancestors about
the cycles of life. And death.
Eliade thought that
understanding our connection
with these cycles, is what
ultimately allowed our minds
and our cultures to evolve.
But the awareness of death
also led to the fear of death.
In trying rationalize
such a huge mystery,
people, you could say,
"invented" God.
Freud also thought
religion came from the need
"to shield ourselves from these
intimidating forces of nature"--
things in life that
are too overwhelming.
So, basically, just like our
ancestors "created" God
out of their fear of death, we
had then "created" "His Voice",
after seeing some damned
fossil that we did not know
how to explain.
According to Pyunma.
Let's say that the
suicide bombers believed
His Voice was divine.
So then, why is it that every
person who has heard it
has gone on to
be a suicide bomber?
It just doesn't make sense.
Well. Stick with me,
because Pyunma's reasoning
gets even stranger.
He says, "in all of history,
no one's murdered more people
for laughs than God."
[DR. GILMORE] I understand.
But even if His Voice
were actually some
kind of divine power,
we mustn't overlook
the possibility
that it's now being exploited
for political gains.
That's true, governments
will exploit religion,
like anything else.
A certain dictator
from my home country
definitely comes to mind.
Actually, one of the more
bizarre rumors surrounding
"the Fuhrer" is that he was
compelled to wage the Holocaust
in the first place after
he had come into posession
of the fossil of an angel.
Hmph.
[HEINRICH] Pyunma had
asked G.B. to research
that particular fossil.
The fact that G.B. has now
also gone missing sounds
like more than a coincidence.
[BOTH]
Hmm...
Heinrich, if what you're
calling "God" is the product
of a mind seeking
answers, then tell me:
How can it intervene
so directly as to incite
suicide bombings,
and to actually make
some people
disappear altogether?
[HEINRICH]
Good question.
As he studied mankind's
origins, Pyunma eventually
began to suspect that,
either through evolution
or maybe the influence
of something else entirely,
our minds had
actually become a God.
[HEINRICH] He wrote, "Could our
human minds--these things that
hold rational thought by some
fluke of nature--could they
themselves be a 'God'?
What if our collective
mind holds some unknown factor
that we've simply called "God"
for lack of a better term?
What if this is the factor
that's allowed us to
adapt, create, survive?"
[FRANCOISE gasps]
[JOE]
How can you be here?
Hi, Joe! You okay?
I've been worried about
you since the other night.
[JOE stammers]
Talk to me.
[JOE sighs]
Yesterday, a lot
of people died here.
[TOMOE gasps]
Oh, no... But
you're okay, right?
I'm the only
one who lived.
[TOMOE] That's weighing
on you, isn't it?
[TOMOE] Don't worry, Joe.
God doesn't bestow burdens
that we can't overcome.
[JOE sighs heavily]
Francoise... Tomoe was
a vision that you sent me.
[thunder rumbling]
If some God really existed
inside each one of us,
maybe it could cause
Pyunma and G.B. to vanish...
Although...
If humanity is being incited
by a God that's within everyone,
then why is it that only
a few have heard His Voice?
And Joe, he never even
saw that angel fossil.
How could he want to
become a suicide bomber?
Hell if I know.
[HEINRICH] But, all throughout
history, hasn't it been the case
that only certain people
would go around claiming
they could hear
the "voice of God"?
People like
"spiritual mediums."
Shamans, ascetics, martyrs;
they'd all claim to commune
with the gods, after
facing "extreme trials."
Today, when adventerous
types like racecar drivers
or astronuasts face
intense overstimulation,
they'll claim to feel some
"heightened sense of awareness."
Maybe all of these
people felt the same thing,
whatever that thing is...
Then Joe, whose brain was
artificially enhanced.
could be prone to some
"heightened awareness" too.
Joe's brain was indeed under
an extreme state of tension
during his leave, which may
well have caused some kind
of synaptic anomaly that, in
time, Joe mistakenly began to
interpret as
"His Voice," perhaps.
[IVAN] "When this exists,
that comes to be;
with the arising
of this, that arises.
When this does not exist,
that does not come to be;
with the cessation
of this, that ceases."
Interesting how sutras even
after the Buddha's time
would imply that
humanity and the divine
have existed side
by side, always;
us not creating it,
nor it us.
[DR. GILMORE &amp; HENRICH]
Hmm...
[distant explosions]
[MAN] Do you have
anything new on "His Voice"?
[JET] Yes, sir.
We need to get the word out
as soon as possible.
[MAN]
About what?
About Samuel Klein.
His whole organization.
They're... They're all
followers of His Voice.
Hm?!
[JET] What that means is,
the entire U.S. Congress...
They're under the
control of His Voice, too!
Oh... And?
[JET gasps]
And now, we have to prepare
countermeasure immediately,
before this gets any
further out of control.
Everyone has
to know that--
I get it. Don't worry about
His Voice, I'll handle it.
But we have to deal with
the Dubai incident first.
[JET gasps]
The man who, made you
a cyborg, Dr. Gilmore...
He's currently operating
out of Istanbul, is he not?
Have you been in
contact with him
or his "Foundation" recently?
What are
you saying?
We've identifided
the two terrorists
responsible for attacking Dubai.
[JET]
Bastard!
[JET grunts]
[blows landing]
[taser crackling]
[JET grunts]
Your old friends are likely
experiencing the same thing
right about now. We thank you
for your service, Agent Link.
You're about to embark
on your final mission.
[JET quietly whimpering]
[JET gasps]
[screaming]
[alarms blaring,
police sirens wailing]
[JET gasps]
[PA SYSTEM] Hostiles closing
in from both ground level
and rooftop. Number: unknown.
[CHANG yells]
Use these. I'll take the
ones coming in from the roof.
Hrrgh!
Urgh!
Pwoogh!
[STAFF scream]
[FEMALE STAFF scream]
Haaah!
[CHANG screams]
[GERONIMO JR.]
Hmph!
Hmph. Rrgh!
[GERONIMO JR. growls]
[GERONIMO JR.]
Rraagh!
Haagh!
[GERONIMO JR.]
Raagh!
[panting]
[GERONIMO JR. roars]
[GUARD A]
Hey!
Hey, y-you all right?!
C'mon, I gotcha.
[GUARD gasps, stutters]
[JET]
Hey!
[radio chatter]
[RADIO] We've sustained
heavy casualties down here!
Right here...
[JET]
Ah! What the hell?!
My God...
[gasps]
[JET] What did they...
make me do?
[indistinct yelling
among OFFICIALS]
Even more people are hearing
this damn voice now.
[GUARD]
Don't move!
I do not have
time for this, kid!
I wish they'd let up already!
How many of these
damn things are there?!
Doctor! I have
a signal from Joe!
What?! Joe is alive?!
Yes. He's sending me
his coordinates right now.
[IVAN] So he wants me to
teleport him back here?
Now I'm getting
a signal from 002!
[FRANCOISE] He's asking that
we open a channel for him.
[JET] Dr. Gilmore,
moments ago, a United States
Naval nuclear subarine
declared their intention
to "help humanity start anew,
in answer to His Voice."
Now, they've gone silent.
The Pentagon and the White House
are scrambling to locate it.
They won't find it.
They're too late.
[DR. GILMORE] What is the U.S.
Government's role in all this?
They wanted to... blame us
Zero-Zero Cyborgs for...
They wanted to blame us
for all of the bombings.
But they can't stop
more from coming...
Doctor, you always believed
that he was the one who could
stop something like
this, didn't you?
Doctor! Before he was
teleported, Joe whispered,
"I know Jet's not our enemy."
And when Joe said he'd
answer His Voice, and...
and help that B-2 pilot...
it was to prove Jet wasn't
involved! Because Joe never
lost faith in his teammate!
In spite of everything,
Joe has only fought for justice!
I know in my heart that
Joe can save us all,
if you'll just believe in him.
[JET grunts]
Now what?
They'll break through...
Hmm.
[HEINRICH gasps]
[CHANG gasps]
[WOMAN whimpers]
[FRANCOISE gasps]
[FRANCOISE]
Joe!
[JOE] I'm so sorry
I made you worry.
I'm glad you're all right.
When the nuke exploded in Dubai,
I was so ashamed that I lived
when all those other
people didn't make it.
But I know why I
really lived now.
It's because of you, Francoise.
And His Voice... I can hear
it in a different way now.
Doctor. I'm going to go stop
that submarine, no matter what.
Can you arrange things?
Hm.
[CHANG] The subarine went
dark fifteen minutes ago.
Even at its top speed,
it can't have gone
any farther than this, right?
[IVAN] Without the submarine's
exact coordinates,
I'm not able to
teleport you inside of it.
But, if they're following
standard procedure,
just like Jet has been
telling us they are,
they'll be launching
their nuclear missiles
in just fifteen minutes!
What are our options?
[FRANCOISE] The U.S.S. Sentinel
carries interceptor missiles.
It's off the
coast of Hawaii.
[DR. GILMORE] All right,
then. We take the ship.
[CREWMAN gasps]
Attention: I'm opening missile
tubes. Prepare to fire...
[SUBMARINE OFFICER]
No!
[OFFICERS grunt]
[GERONIMO JR. growls]
[CHANG]
You all right?!
[GERONIMO JR. grunts]
The nukes haven't launched yet?
[IVAN] No, not yet, Doctor. The
deployment of nuclear missiles
requires multiple
authorizations. It's possible
there's some unrest within
the submarine's crew.
[HEINRICH] I'd really
like to trust you guys.
Unfortunately, I cannot.
They fired them!
[FRANCOISE]
Six... Five... Four...
Intercepting targets now!
It worked?!
[JOE gasps]
[FRANCOISE]
One left...
We missed the last nuke!
Francoise...
You can calculate the
missile's trajectory, right?
[JOE] It looks like we'll have
to detonate it. Manually.
And you're going to do it
yourself? Joe, you can't!
Even if you succeed, you won't
make it down from that altitude!
I know that.
Then, why?!
Francoise. My life was spared
so that I could do this.
[FRANCOISE quietly whimpers]
[FRANCOISE] Ivan.
Please teleport Joe
to the coordintes I'm sending.
[IVAN] Are you positive,
Francoise? I won't have
the strength for another
teleportation after this.
[FRANCOISE]
Please...
[JOE gasps]
[HEINRICH]
It's still there!
Joe!
[FRANCOISE sobs quietly,
HEINRICH sighs]
[BOTH gasp]
Something is closing in on it!
[JOE gasps]
[JOE] Jet! What are
you doing here?!
[JET] I've been listening in on
the brainwave transmissions.
Give me the charges!
[BOTH grunt]
[JOE] Forget it! There's still
time for you to make it back!
[JET] Joe, even if you stop
the nuke, there's no guarantee
you'll stop His Voice.
Are you sure you want
to go through with this?
[JOE] Everyone answers
His Voice differently,
based on their frame of mind.
If we show people
they can stand up to
this kind of answer,
they might join us
in fighting for peace!
[JET] And you believe that's
what His Voice really wanted?
[JOE] Maybe. Enough to know that
this is the right decision!
[BOTH grunt]
[grunting continues]
[JOE grunts]
[JET yells]
[JOE] We did it!
Jet, I'm on!
[JOE gasps]
No! Jet!!
[JOE groans]
[JOE] It's true, people
can be foolish...
In groups, we easily
get corrupted
by some collective mind...
One that we can't
seem to resist.
We aren't perfect,
but that means we also
have so much potential.
We've done terrible things
together, but we can do
great together as well.
That's what makes us worth it!
Are you really going
to crush the hopes
of all the people who've risked
everything, risked their lives,
trying to answer your
call to save this world?!
How can you look down on
all that's good about us
and destroy us anyway?!
Give me an answer...
...God!
[IVAN grunts softly
in his sleep]
[soft grunting continues]
[FRANCOISE sobs softly]
[grunting]
[startled gasp]
[JOE sighs]
[JOE]
Hmm...
[JOE gasps]
[door creaking open]
Ah. Good,
you're up.
Yeah, but where are we?
This place? We're
in my safe house.
Safe house?
What am I doing here? Francoise,
how did I get back down?
[FRANCOISE] I guess...
it's a mystery.
But the very fact
that you're here
means He answered
you this time.
Didn't the missile--?
Wait, where's Jet?!
[GREAT BRITAIN]
Pyunma? Fancy that.
[PYUNMA] I know. I found
myself here when I came to.
[JET] And where
exactly is "here?"
Well, if you guys made it,
maybe it's Heaven?
[DR. GILMORE] No. This is
the exact same world
you boys helped save.
It's good to have
you back with us.
You should know that I
am very proud of you all.
How'd we get here?
"His Voice" did this?
Who knows? Maybe we're all here
because someone who had heard
His Voice asked loud enough.
Even if that's true, what the
hell are we supposed to do next?
This isn't over.
The fighting will only continue.
Our world has indeed
been gravely affected
by the atrocities commited
in answer to "His Voice."
So then, doesn't that make
it all the more necessary
that you continue to
fight for the justice
you have always believed in?
[bells ringing,
children laughing]
[FRANCOISE] You know, as I
watched those shooting stars,
I thought, maybe...
His Voice doesn't
bestow burdens
that humanity
can't overcome.
[JOE gasps]
And that maybe those
"angels" are monuments
to every one of the people
who've heard His Voice
and sacrificed themselves
to do what was right.