[Narrator] The orb had
incarnated several times
before transforming into a boy.
That boy then
encountered a young girl
from Ninannah named March.
She named him Fushi.
He fought a battle
against the bear, Oniguma.
Through that stimulation,
Fushi was able to
acquire new information
about the world around him.
Thank you for the food.
(opening theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
Listen.
No, one's allowed to see
the two of us playing this game.
You have to obey the
rules or you lose.
Hide here until I
come back, okay?
But sister-
[Sister] Here's some food,
and you can eat berries
here in the woods
if you run out.
(girl gasps)
Wait, big sister!
[Big Sister] Stay hidden!
I'll make you a new stuffed doll
if you win the game.
[Woman] Parona!
Where have you been
all week, child?
Where did my big sister go?
[Woman] She's not here anymore.
She was chosen to be the
sacrifice to the god Oniguma.
(Paruna gasps)
[Paruna] Big sister!
[Village Man] Running
away from the Ritual?
What a coward you are,
and you call yourself
a woman of Ninannah?
[Paruna] Big sister!
[Village Man] You aren't a
part of this village anymore.
Go on, get out of here!
(Paruna pants and gasps)
(Paruna gasps awake)
I was dreaming.
But, a part of me still wonders
what kind of face she
made when she left.
A Large Vessel
(wheels rattle)
[Fushi] Thank you.
(fruit crunches)
For the food.
(March giggles)
You're really funny, puppy.
Here.
(fruit crunches)
[Fushi] Thank you for the food.
So can you tell me how
much further we're going?
We're going all
the way to Yanome.
It should take another
20 days to get there.
Hold on a minute.
You're a Yanome shaman, right?
Why do they have you riding
in this prison wagon with us?
Yeah.
You're a really horrible person!
You're the one who got
me into this whole mess.
Why'd you even choose
me in the first place?
Because you were
the prettiest girl
in the whole bunch, actually.
Oh.
Really?
Look, I'm also a
Yanome prisoner.
These people are
desperate in their desire
to satisfy their greed.
They even created a fake shaman
to help them get
away with murder.
But why?
Yanome covets the lush land
Ninannah has developed.
Do you understand?
That's why they became involved
with the sacrifice tradition
in the first place.
[Paruna] Hm?
They help with the ritual
and show their gratitude
by providing supplies.
Then they flatter the populace.
People of Ninannah, thank you
for protecting all of
humanity from Oniguma.
Once your people buy
into their praise,
all that's left is
psychological manipulation,
and occupation.
I had no idea.
I'm disgusted this
horrible ritual
was allowed to go
on all these years.
Children murdered
under the pretense
of some phony tradition.
You don't say?
I thought the people of Ninannah
were faithful and
steadfast in their beliefs.
Even if it meant sacrificing
some of their own.
The grownups still
believe those things.
They don't care about
all the suffering
other people have
endured because of it.
This is insanity.
We need to end this
terrible custom immediately.
That won't happen.
Ninannah's elders are
terribly old fashioned.
Trust me,
they wouldn't believe you
if you stood up and told
them their god is dead.
Their god?
So what can we do?
(March wails)
Stop it, don't don't
do that, puppy!
-What's wrong?
-(liquid sloshes)
(March wails)
It's so stinky I think
I'm gonna throw up.
Look out, it's coming this way.
(March and Parona groan)
[March] Bad puppy!
(water sloshes)
(soft music)
Puppy, you have
to wash off, too.
It's cold, but don't be scared.
I'll go in with you.
(Wolf laps water)
(Wolf whines)
[Fushi] Remember.
Remember me.
Forever.
(whoosh effect)
(water splashes)
Oh, my!
(soft music)
I knew that was gonna be you.
(March laughs)
I missed you.
Wait a minute, March.
You know who this person?
Yeah, this is my friend, Fushi.
We need to get on the
road before it gets dark.
(leash squeaks)
No, Fushi, not that way.
You need to come with me.
(Fushi breathes softly)
(March chuckles)
All right, that's a good boy.
I'll have to teach you how
to use the potty later, too.
Why does he go along and do
everything you tell him to?
Fushi looks like he's grown up,
but he's still a little boy.
So I decided I'm
gonna be his mommy
and teach him things
for when he gets bigger.
(cart rumbles)
[Pioran] She named him Fushi
because he's immortal, huh?
I think it's too bad for
him that he can't die
like the rest of us.
(Pioran and March gasp)
Most humans, they try
to achieve something
for themselves over the
course of their life.
What purpose are they
supposed to find?
If there's no end
point to their life,
and they go on living forever...
A purpose?
(gasps) Oh, sorry.
It's wrong of me
to demand purpose
in another person's life.
(chains rattle)
I don't understand
what you said,
but I am feeling really
happy about things right now.
Hm.
(crickets chirp)
(soft footsteps)
Here, I want you to wear these.
Are these Yanome clothes?
There's even some for little Fu.
You have to put these on.
Arms over your head.
All right, so what
happens to us now?
Now you both have new lives.
As of today, you
are March and Parona
of the nation of Yanome.
(soft music)
(March gasps)
Just look!
See all that yummy looking food?
So many pretty things! (laughs)
Go ahead and help yourselves
to whatever you'd like.
And don't worry,
I'll pay for it.
You mean it?
(March sniffs)
Mm smells so good. (giggles)
(soft music)
(twinkling music)
(crowd chatters)
(soft footsteps)
[Letter Shop Owner]
Now's the time.
Is there anything
you'd like to say
to those you love?
Come on up.
Bring your letters!
-[March] Hey, stop!
-We'll deliver your messages,
-[March] Look over there!
-For you!
Welcome folks.
I'm here to help.
Write what you want to say here.
Write?
What's that?
[Scribe] Oh, I see.
I'll write your message for you.
You just tell me what
it is you want to say.
Oh, let me see.
Mama and Papa, how are you?
Guess where I am now?
I'm here in Yanome.
Don't worry about me, okay?
The end.
Okay, now who should
I deliver this to?
To my Mama and Papa.
They live in Ninannah.
What, Ninannah, are you serious?
That means they're in the
sacred land of Oniguma!
Yup, that's right.
March, Ninannah doesn't
have any reading or writing.
Your parents won't
understand it.
You mean well, but this
just isn't going to work.
They can't read your letter.
Huh?
Well I won't just give up.
I know a different
kind of writing.
Really, March?
What does that
writing look like?
Uh...
(chais rattle)
Hah!
It looks like this!
Yeah?
And what exactly does that say?
It obviously says
March is doing great.
That's what.
Of course it does.
Would you please
send this for me?
Sure.
Where in Ninannah do
you want me to send it?
Like I said, send
it to Mama and Papa.
Yes, but which
district and street?
Whose jurisdiction?
Uh.
Sissy, do you know?
Sorry.
Ninannah's pretty big.
The nearest district
alone has 40 settlements,
And that's just one of many.
What is that a drawing of?
(paper rustles)
Why don't we have dinner
and figure this out later?
(March whimpers softly)
I'll just hold onto
this letter for you.
We'll come back here
when we find out where
your Mama and Papa live.
[March] Okay, then.
(liquid sloshes)
(munching sounds)
What is this stuff,
it's so good?
Hm?
Do you see the weird
way she eats her food?
(both giggle)
Thank you for the food.
This is your mother
speaking, Fushi.
It's very important that
you mind your manners.
Remember what I said?
You have to eat your food
with your hands, like this.
(both slurp noodles)
Have you got it?
March, you need to
mind your manners.
And while you're at it,
use those chopsticks
on your headband.
What do you mean, chopsticks?
These things up here are
very special head scratchers.
You use them when your
head's very, very itchy.
Well, it seems
that certain parts
of Yanome's culture haven't been
properly passed
down to Ninannah.
I must apologize.
Please continue to do
whatever you were doing.
(tense music)
Eat however you like,
my little puppy, Fushi.
(Fushi chokes)
(alarmed shouts)
Are you all right, Fushi?
What happened?
(Fushi gasps)
(Fushi chomps)
(March gasps)
He learns quickly.
He's picked up the
Yanome way of eating.
So what do you think, March?
Yanome is a fine
nation, don't you agree?
Now that you've seen it,
wouldn't it be nice to spend
the rest of your life here?
No, not really.
I don't feel very good.
Huh?
What's going on?
(giggles) Don't
fight it, ladies.
(pensive music)
(both thud)
(Fushi groans)
Even you?
That Western morning
glory is very effective.
(slurps soup)
(Fushi thuds)
As I said in my report,
for the first time in the
long history of the ritual,
we finally laid eyes on Oniguma.
Through a series of
unexpected events,
we were able to capture him.
And on that subject,
there's something else
I'd like to show you.
Take a look at that boy.
(soft music)
As we were about to leave
the arena, he showed up.
And after an extensive
and bloody battle,
he defeated Oniguma.
Unbelievable!
That little boy?
Yes, because he's immortal.
(door scrapes)
[Guard] Go on!
(prisoner gasps)
Sorry about this kid.
But if I kill you, I
walk free. (screams)
(laughs then gasps) His wound!
That's impossible!
(high pitched tone)
(somber music)
(prisoner gasps and screams)
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
It hurts.
(woman screams)
I can't take it!
I just want to get
out of this place,
find a lover,
eat a lot of good food!
-It hurts.
-And have some fun!
-So would you help
me out here and die, please?
Incredible, is he a god,
or some kind of a monster?
Who knows?
However I do believe one thing.
I believe that his
power is unlimited,
and that one way or another
he's essential to
Yanome's future.
[Guard] Move it, you old hag!ú
(rapid footsteps)
Go on, before I
lob your head off.
(whoosh effect)
(guards gasp)
(dramatic music)
(arrow snaps)
(wolf whimpers)
(knives stab)
(door creaks)
-Wha? Fushi!
-It hurts.
Listen March.
You have to talk to him
and make sure he behaves.
-Be strong, Fu.
-[Fushi] It hurts.
They shot you on purpose.
They're gonna pay for this, Fu.
It's gonna be all right.
I'll take care of you.
There, there.
See that?
You're all better.
Nothing to it, you
did good, Fushi.
[Parona] March,
is Fushi with you?
Sissy?
Where are you?
(birds flap and screech)
[Paruna] March, I'm up here.
Sissy!
What have you got in your room?
Not much, straw,
a pot,
and this. That's it.
(soft music)
Okay, tie the
arrow to the strip.
Do you know where
we are exactly?
And what it is they're
planning to do with us?
Don't worry March.
It'll be fine.
Now listen, could you gather
up some of Fushi's fur?
Sure, but what for?
[Guard] A little
more to the right.
Keep going.
(March gasps and pants)
Hey, mister.
I need to ask you something.
When do we get to leave?
[Guard] You're
staying here forever.
(cart rattles)
It hurts.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
(scratches ground)
Hey, what's wrong, Fu?
You're wound's all
better, isn't it?
It hurts, it hurts.
What is it, Fu?
(soft music)
(ground crumbles)
[Fushi] It hurts it hurts.
(Fushi growls)
It hurts.
It hurts it hurts.
Huh, what is this?
(March strains)
-It hurts.
-(March shouts)
An arrow?
(gasps) You mean
these are all arrows?
That poor animal.
We have to try and
make him better.
[Hayase] How are
things progressing?
[Guard] Not so well.
Nobody wants to
get near Oniguma.
Oh, please. How difficult can
it be to take care of a bear?
Wait, we should have her do it.
(paws tap)
[Guard] Are you sure?
It's dangerous.
It'll be fine.
She's nothing but an
imprisoned little girl.
It won't matter if she dies.
[Paruna] I can't believe
she's going to make you
take care of that bear.
It's too dangerous a
job to do by yourself.
I have both Fushi
and Kanitaro with me,
so I'll be all right.
I can hear you moving
around up there.
You're doing cleaning
right, Sissy?
You hang in there.
[Paruna] Yeah, but listen.
Don't worry about me.
First, I'm going to
pretend to be Yanome
with that old lady's help.
(old woman screams)
Help me I'm dying here.
(mop thuds)
[Paruna] And then,
we'll help you.
[Together] We did it!
[Paruna] We'll kill Oniguma,
and we'll bring home
its hide and eyes
as proof of its death.
Then I'm sure the people
of Ninannah will agree.
We don't need to carry out
the disgusting ritual anymore.
(somber music)
I think we can do this.
No, we have to do
it, no matter what.
Isn't that right, big sister?
(somber music)
[March] You're just like me.
I know you are.
People in my village
all got together
and said I was
special and amazing
when I had to leave Ninannah.
But I knew I was just me.
Just a little girl.
It hurts it hurts.
You're just a giant bear
who likes eating human meat.
You can't really help it.
People made a big
fuss about you,
they hunted you and
shot you full of arrows.
And that's how you ended
up looking like this.
Hurts.
I'm gonna fix you up.
You can go home when
your wounds heal.
Won't that be nice?
Hey, sorry if I
made you feel upset.
I didn't mean to.
It's going to be all right.
There, there, you'll see.
You'll be fine, really.
It hurts it hurts.
(dramatic music)
Thank you so much.
Huh?
(dramatic music)
(somber music)
[Narrator] And then,
the vessel opened.
(wind howls)
(Paruna grunts)
[Paruna] Onigumo is dead.
They'll come and retrieve
the body by tomorrow.
We need to escape
with the proof first.
We'll be out of here
in no time, March.
You won't need to become a
grownup in this damn place.
(Paruna gasps)
(spar snaps)
(Paruna whimpers)
(rope scrapes)
Over there
Big sister!
It hurts.
[Paruna] What happened?
Looks like I'm in
a storage room.
[Guard] Look who it is,
and in a place you're
not supposed to be.
I don't have to tell anyone
you tried to run away.
As long as you do what I say.
(Paruna grunts)
(guard shouts)
(fist thuds)
You dare attack me?
I won't tell anyone, as long
as you do what I say.
Shift's over.
(footsteps approach)
You!
What do you want?
I'm taking you with me.
(triumphant music)
Big sister.
I bet you were smiling,
when you ran away too.
Weren't you?
I want you to know I'm
going to make good use
of the life you gave me.
Time to escape.
Coming Sissy!
(closing theme music)
Preview
[Narrator] Parona
gathers up the others
and they leave the prison,
implementing their plan
to return to Ninannah
but a squad of
soldiers from Yanome
led by Hayase mercilessly
Those Who Follow