(dramatic orchestral music)
[The Beholder] I am the
one who created you.
We have a grand objective
behind all of this.
We are attempting to
preserve this world.
The entity that attacked you
was sent to this world
to impede our objective.
(mystical music)
Farewell, Fushi.
We shall have fun.
Until the coming end.
(opening theme music)
-(crickets chirping)
-(animals vocalizing)
[Gugu] I've been
thinking lately...
How did I end up
being me anyway?
Why wasn't I born
into the family
in that mansion over there?
I feel the same way as you.
But think about it.
That's why the
two of us brothers
are working so hard every day.
Am I right?
First, we're gonna
save up a ton of money.
Then someday...
we'll be able to live together
in a huge house like that one.
Yeah.
The Boy Who Wants to Change
(soft music)
(birds whistling)
All right. Time to work!
Shin, you're in
the fields today.
Gugu, go to the market
and sell these vegetables.
Sell every last one, okay?
Yes sir, I'll do it!
(crowd chattering)
I have fresh produce here!
Come and get your
fresh vegetables!
(gasps)
That girl's always here.
I wonder what her name is.
Maybe she's from
that big mansion.
Tell me something, kid.
Do you sell seeds here?
Sorry, sir, I don't have any.
I'll ask my master if
he plans to carry those.
[Old Man] You do
that, young man.
Bye, now!
Wow, that old fart's
just as weird as ever.
You mean you know him?
Yeah, he's the beer brewer
who lives at the
top of the hill.
I heard he's involved
in some illegal stuff.
(gentle instrumental music)
Big Bro, I'm home!
I got some leftovers
from the market!
Good luck. You'd
better win tomorrow.
[Shin] I hear ya. Bye.
Who were they?
Some friends of mine.
I just got to know
them recently.
Yeah?
Hold on...
Some coins are missing.
Hey, did you take some of our
money out of here, Big Bro?
Now why would I do that?
I don't know, but some of
it is definitely missing.
Wait a minute.
Do you think those guys
might have done it?
You're not accusing
my friends, are you?
No, I didn't mean to say...
Sorry 'bout that.
I just heard there were
some sketchy people
in the neighborhood.
So...
Sure looks like we've
been robbed, though.
Well, not much we
can do about it.
Don't get too upset, bro.
Yeah. I guess you're right.
We can just keep on
working and earn it again.
I'm gonna hide it
up here from now on.
[Shin] Okay.
[Gugu] So, do you want
half of the steamed bun
I got at the market?
I'm good.
Huh?
(soft music)
(dog whimpering)
Are you hungry, little buddy?.
Want to share a steamed bun?
Here you go. Eat up.
Things suck for both of us, huh?
(crowd chattering)
Get your fresh vegetables here!
Hey! I know you!
You're the dog from yesterday!
Sorry, buddy, I don't have
any steamed buns today.
Hm?
Meer.
I didn't see that before.
Your name's Meer, huh?
Meer!
-It's her!
-Meer!
(Meer barking)
Uh..
Uh, pardon me.
Is this the dog
you're looking for?
Hm?
Yes!
Meer, how I've missed you!
Don't ever run off again!
(sighing)
I should thank you somehow.
So here's a token
of my gratitude.
Are you sure you want
to do that, Miss?
It was a gift from your father.
It's fine.
Father bought it for me,
knowing I don't like
to wear this color.
If you sell this ring,
you will never ever
have to sell veggies
at this market again.
(gasps)
She's seen me! She
knows who I am!
Can I ask what your name is?
[Handmaiden] That was a rude
thing to say to him, Miss.
[Girl] Oh, don't be silly.
I was just trying
to cheer him up.
Oh boy.
(upbeat instrumental music)
Hey, Big Bro, I'm home!
I had a really good day today!
Hm?
Big Bro?
Brother!
Huh?
(voice shaking)
[Shin] There's a thing
called fate in this world.
I'm going to change mine and
fight for something better.
I needed the money
to start a new life.
Sorry, Gugu.
(emotional music)
[Gugu] What a liar.
(digging)
How did I end up
being me anyway?
[Girl] If you sell this ring,
you will never ever
have to sell veggies
at this market again.
(clattering)
Huh?
If I crashed into that thing,
like bam, tumble, kaboom,
would it change my fate?
Nah. That's ridiculous.
What the heck am I thinking?
(suspenseful music)
(log slams)
(gulps)
Hey kid! Are you all right?
One, two...
(groaning)
This damn thing
just won't budge.
I gotta get some
help to move it.
Would you mid keeping
an eye on this?
Huh?
Uh...
(sighs)
That was so dangerous.
He was going too fast.
Oh wow, I could have
actually been killed.
(cracking)
(suspenseful music)
Huh?
Hey!
You down there! Look
out for the log!
(gasps)
(suspenseful music)
You've got to get
out of the way! Run!
(gasps)
(intense music)
Somebody..
help me.
(log slams)
[Man] Did the log hit
her? She's bleeding!
[Man] Do something!
Tend her wounds!
[Woman] Look! She's
opening her eyes!
[Man] Rean! Hang in
there, sweetheart!
Help me carry her!
(soft music)
[Gugu] Oh, so that's it.
Her name's Rean, huh?
That was a close call.
Thank goodness she's safe.
Thank goodness.
[Woman] What should I do, sir?
[Man] We're taking her
back to the mansion.
You go on ahead and
get hold of the doctor!
Have him meet us there!
[Woman] Yes, sir!
(crickets chirping)
(emotional music)
(mysterious music)
(groaning)
Where am I?
I can't stand up straight.
What's going on?
My belly's sticking out.
(gasps)
(soft music)
My eyes..
My mouth..
My nose...
What's happened?
I look like...
Well, your nose was destroyed,
but you're still able to eat!
I'm surprised you're alive,
considering what
you went through.
When you think about
it, you're pretty lucky!
[Gugu] What a cruel joke.
I always dreamed of living
as someone who wasn't me.
And suddenly, that
dream has come true.
Except now, I'm some kind
of monster who isn't me.
Did you hear the latest?
That freaky old brewer
finally made himself a monster
and it's living with him!
(sweeping)
Hey, I'm back!
Where's the old man?
Look...
Both of you owe me a
great debt of gratitude.
I've brought an
extraordinary gift for you.
Allow me to present...
an immortal freak!
(soft music)
(whooshing)
Look at that! Isn't it amazing?
And you're positive that
thing's immortal, huh?
Well, I'll be!
That is way over my puny brain.
Where in the world
did you even find
something like this, old lady?
Members of the Yanome
Guard captured it.
We went through a lot
together, and now it's with me.
(whooshing)
[Gugu] Excuse me.
I'm...
My name is Gugu.
I'm a servant here.
What's your name?
What's name?
I can tell you.
His name is Fushi.
[Gugu] Fushi? Because
you're immortal?
That's so on-the-nose!
(laughing)
Huh?
Did anybody ever tell
you you're weird?
Well, whatever.
So hey, Booze Man, do you
mind if I show him around?
Fine.
[Gugu] You two are gonna
be staying with us, huh?
I've been living here for
almost three months now.
I got hurt real bad,
and that's when Booze Man
came along and helped me.
I gotta tell you, he's a strange
old coot, that's for sure.
I call him Booze Man
because he makes homemade
liquor in these vats.
He doesn't have
too many customers
because his product is
such an acquired taste.
Look. This is where he
does the distilling.
What is it?
[Gugu] Hm?
What is this...
liquor?
[Gugu] Oh, right.
(liquid pouring)
Here, drink this.
(spits and coughs)
(laughing)
Hm.
I just noticed you and your
clothes are pretty filthy.
You can't go out in
public like that.
Hey, where are you two going?
[Gugu] We're gonna
go play in the water!
Hm?
What's wrong?
You're afraid of the
forest, aren't you?
[Gugu] Why would he be afraid?
We were attacked by
something unknown
when we were
traveling through it.
It was a terrifying creature
that looked just like a tree.
[Gugu] Hm.
And you're still afraid,
even though you're immortal?
I'm scared.
It's all right. I'm
gonna watch out for you.
I'm scared.
We'll probably get in trouble
for using this water,
but what the heck.
Hey, wait a minute.
How can you be wounded?
I thought you were immortal.
You don't know why either, huh?
Well, when you don't know
the answer to a question,
you can say, "I don't know."
[Fushi] I don't know.
[Gugu] That was fast.
You catch on pretty quick!
Okay, let's get
these clothes off.
I'll wash them for you.
Huh?
This thing's stuck to you.
And this, too!
And this!
What's going on?
Hey! What are you doing?
I don't need to undress!
I'm very ugly!
Stop it!
See?
Aren't I ugly?
Huh?
Well, say something.
What does the word "ugly" mean?
[Gugu] A face that's
terrible to look at is ugly.
I'm called a monster by
normal-looking people.
Guys like me are forced
to spend our lives
hiding from everyone.
I understand why,
but I still haven't gotten
used to living this way.
[Fushi] Ug-uh-ly!
(sighs)
[Gugu] Well, since
we're both monsters,
we might as well stick together.
[Fushi] Ug-uh-ly.
(bouncy music)
Listen up, Fushi.
We need to have a
talk about the future.
If you're gonna live here,
you have to learn how to do
some work around the place.
Damn it! Say yes or something!
If you're gonna be human,
you have to learn
to answer people.
Yes.
[Gugu] Good.
First thing in the morning,
when you wake up,
you clean the floors.
Yes.
[Gugu] After that,
you cook breakfast.
Yes.
[Gugu] You work the fields.
After that, we man the shop.
Yes.
[Gugu] Fushi, you're bigger
than me, so tell me this...
How old are you?
I don't know.
[Gugu] Interesting.
You don't know anything
about yourself, huh?
So what about your
parents, then?
Do you know what they look like?
I don't know.
What is parent?
You really don't know
anything, do you?
Well, a parent is someone
who loves you no matter what
and always takes care of you.
Tell me about family.
Did you have
sisters or brothers?
I don't know.
[Gugu] I had someone
until not too long ago.
An awesome older brother.
He's out making money right now.
He's gonna come home rich
someday, I just know it.
I guess you're lucky that you
don't know about your family.
That way, they can
never disappoint you.
You'll never have to lose hope.
I envy you.
(crickets chirping)
[Old Woman] So what do you
think we should do about him
from this point forward?
Hey, I'm just a brewer, my dear.
What do you want me to tell you?
His powers are too special.
I'm sure countries
would go to war
to exploit him as a weapon.
[Gugu] You might
be right, old man.
But if it came to that,
I'd do everything I
could to protect him.
What's the big deal?
There must be plenty
of people out there
who'd be willing to buy him
off us for lots of cash!
[Gugu] Stop it!
Don't talk about selling Fushi!
I have an idea!
Let's use him to make
immortality wine!
I'll chop off his
fingers to make the base!
[Gugu] That's not
funny, Booze Man!
Don't say things like that!
(laughing)
What are you so upset
about?. I was just kidding!
You're such a serious boy.
[Old Woman] Fine, then.
If we can't do the wine,
we'll have him make some side
money as a street performer.
[Old Man] That sounds
like an excellent idea!
Why are you two being so greedy?
Listen to you!
We're not using
Fushi to make money!
That's disgusting!
Listen to me, you two!
Fushi's more than just
some weird creature
who can transform in an instant!
He has a precious power,
and we should protect him!
We should be glad he's here!
I want him to be
part of our family!
I mean...
he's like a brother to me.
You mean your older brother?
[Gugu] Younger brother!
[Fushi] Yum. Yummy.
(birds whistling)
[Gugu] So tell me, Fushi...
what do you think you'll
be doing in 10 years?
I don't understand.
[Gugu] I mean, when I stop to
consider the possibilities,
I think I'll still be
living like I am now.
Cleaning, cooking, working.
A boring life.
I wasn't always like this..
Before my accident, I had dreams
of living in a big mansion
and eating a bellyful
of food every day.
Well, as things turned
out, that dream came true.
But it came at a
pretty steep cost.
Back in my old life, I
had a cool big brother,
and I even got to talk face to
face with this girl I liked.
But that life is gone, and
it's never coming back.
Not ever.
That means no matter what
I do or how hard I try,
my future is set in stone.
It's pretty depressing.
But things are different
now that you showed up.
Thanks to you being here,
I think I can put up
with all this boredom.
How does this power
of yours work?
For instance, if you were
to turn into Booze Man
would you think booze
tastes good then?
I do not know.
[Gugu] That would be fun.
You should try it out.
So how would I do that?
Excuse me...
Welcome! Thank you
for stopping by!
(light music)
So let me ask, what
brings you here today?
This is a brewery, you know!
(gasps)
Uh.. I know that.
But I'm not here for that stuff!
I don't want to buy
liquor or anything!
I'm looking for something
a lot more healthy!
[Gugu] Let's see now..
We do have some
supplemental drinks, but...
Oh, I know!
Why don't I bring you
some of our non-alcoholic
sweet pickles?
They're pretty tasty
when you combine them
with water and citrus!
That sounds fantastic!
Will those pickles
heal my wound?
[Gugu] Your wound?
Unfortunately, the injury
I suffered three months ago
still hasn't healed yet.
It's a really big,
embarrassing wound,
so I've been forced to hide it.
[Gugu] Then let's get that
wound fixed up for you
right this minute!
Great!
[Gugu] She's so cute!
I'm so glad this turned out
to be such a friendly shop!.
Just between you and me,
I always thought it'd
be a really scary place.
For instance, what is
up with your head thing?
Why do you wear it everywhere?
Ugly.
[Gugu] Actually, it's
for attracting customers!
Who would have thought?
People just love it!
(giggles)
It is kind of adorable!
[Gugu] I am so happy right now!
No, be careful!
I've gotta be careful
to always know my place.
Hey.
You guys don't happen to be
related to the brewer, do you?
[Gugu] No! We just work here.
Oh!
Does that mean you'll definitely
be here whenever I come in?
[Gugu] Of course! We work
the fields in the morning,
and we're here in the afternoon.
I was wondering...
You mind if I ask your name?
[Gugu] Um..
Well, uh...
my name's...
Gugu.
Oh, not you.
I was asking this guy.
-That's Fushi.
Oh! Fushi, you say?
Interesting. That's a
very beautiful name.
How old are you? Where
do you come from?
What is it you like to eat for
breakfast, lunch, and dinner?
[Gugu] Nice of you to ask!
He likes everything
I make for him!
I like fruit.
What a coincidence! I do too!
[Gugu] Fushi!. We're
in the middle of work!
Please, just call me Rean.
Rean.
You're swell!
Rean, Rean.
(giggling)
-Rean, Re-
-Oh, you!
[Gugu] All right, that's enough!
Go help the old
man or something.
You're going to distract
the other customers!
Come back!
I'd like to go for a
little walk with Fushi,
if you don't mind.
That way, we won't
be distracting
the other customers, right?
[Gugu] No!
Listen, the boy can't even take
his clothes off without help!
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
He can barely even speak yet.
He's still like a baby!
He needs to be educated
in just about everything,
and he certainly doesn't
have time to play!
Oh, well that's no big deal.
I could teach him how to talk.
And most certainly how to
remove all of his clothes.
I'm just kidding!
(sniffling)
I have to say, man lives
not only for booze alone.
Booze can certainly make
a person feel happy,
at least in the short run.
But after a time,
you begin to see
that you need more
to nurture you.
[Gugu] What are you
talking about, old man?
I don't even drink booze!
I'm saying the time you spend
dejected is time well spent.
It helps to develop
your personality.
It makes you that much more
of a well-rounded human being.
[Gugu] Hm?
Embrace the heartache.
It will help you to
become an even better man.
Trust me, Gugu.
(light music)
(breathing heavily)
(grunting)
What are you doing?
[Gugu] I'm working out, Fushi.
I'm trying to become something
worth being attracted to.
Me, too. I work out, too.
[Gugu] You don't need
to be doing this!
Just get down!
Just go back inside
and get some sleep.
(crickets chirping)
Look at that. What's
gotten into Gugu I wonder.
Good for the little man!
He wants to become stronger.
Yeah, go, kid!
Give 'em what for!
(laughing)
(groaning)
Preview
(soft orchestral music)
[The Beholder] As
they continue leading
their peaceful life in
Takunaha, Gugu and Fushi
gradually come to understand
each other better.
The Two Monsters