[The Beholder] There
is a common experience
shared by evolved beings
within this reality.
They are challenged by
those who stand in the way
of their continued existence,
taking and destroying
what comprises them,
restricting what they can do.
I do not think highly
of these attempts
to subvert the use of free will.
This freedom to choose
is a sacred thing
that should be given
to all sentient beings.
(opening theme music)
(Gugu gasps)
(Gugu screams)
New Family
[Gugu] Fushi!
[Fushi] Gugu, you need to run!
(air whooshing)
(Fushi groaning)
[Gugu] Wait, isn't that?
We were attacked by
something unknown
when we walked
through the forest,
it was a terrifying creature
that looked just like a tree.
I'm telling you,
get out of here!
[Gugu] No way! I
want to help you!
-(Gugu grunts)
-(dramatic music)
(monster roaring)
(Gugu screams)
[Gugu] Fushi!
(Fushi panting)
(Gugu shouts)
(Fushi Monster groans)
Bull's-eye!
(screams)
Gugu!
(Gugu screaming)
(Gugu gagging)
[Gugu] The liquor...
Fushi...
Great, what am I
supposed to do now?
(fire whooshes)
Ow! What the hell?
Where'd this come from?
Now I understand,
the fire was able to spread
from the liquor I barfed up.
I have a great idea!
-(dramatic music)
-(Gugu panting)
(spikes clashing)
Good, it's distracted by Fushi.
Now's my chance!
All I have to do is
bear down on my belly
and I'll puke it out!
(exhales)
huh? What's going on?
I didn't have any problem
getting it to come out earlier.
(coughs)
Oh no! I must be empty!
[Wolf Fushi] Stop, Gugu!
[Gugu] Fushi!
Listen, run away Gugu,
or I'll get angry!
Get out of here, now!
Go! Get moving!
-(spikes clashing)
-Hang in there!
I'll be back in five minutes!
Don't do it!
If you come back
here, I will bite you!
[Gugu] Works for me!
(Gugu panting)
I'll get back to Booze
Man's place in one minute,
and come back with
a bellyful of liquor
in a couple of minutes.
I'm coming to help, Fushi!
What's wrong?
Of course. It's the booze.
Get up. (groaning)
You have to move!
You've got to hold
it together, Gugu!
At this point, you're the
only one who can save Fushi!
There it is!
Keep going!
Good!
Finally. Almost there.
(Rean gasps excitedly)
Hold on!
You're the one who kicked
me and ran off with Rean!
-Huh?
-Really?
Are you responsible?
Did you get my daughter to
run away from her family?
Stop! I already told you!
I decided to run away on my own!
None of these people had
anything to do with it!
Oh, please! What did
you do to my daughter?
Sorry, Gugu.
I had no idea my father would
come all the way out here.
You know what?
We should just go, dear.
It's already pretty late.
What's the matter, Gugu?
Something seems off.
(Gugu grunting)
[Gugu] Gimme some
booze, old man!
Fill me up, and make
sure it's really strong!
Huh?
(all gasping softly)
(Gugu laughing)
Looks like you've
already been drinking!
What the hell's
gotten into you, Gugu?
What do you think's
gotten into me?!
The booze you put in my belly!
It's all gone, and
I need a refill!
And don't give me any of
that cheap crap you sell!
Give me the strongest shit
you've got, you understand?!
Oh my! What a horrid little boy!
Stop it! What's
going on with you?!
What in the world's happened?
Where's Fushi?!
[Gugu] Huh?
Fushi's in the forest!
Things are going boom!
Like vwoom, vwoom!
He's in trouble!
There's no time to waste!
I gotta get back
there and help him!
Old man, leave it alone.
Let me take care of this.
Do as he says. Don't
ask any questions.
Hmm, whatever you say.
Hopefully, this
will do the trick.
This liquor's been
distilled over and over,
it's the strongest
stuff I've ever made.
(Gugu coughing)
I was afraid of that.
It looks to me like there
might be a rupture somewhere.
We need to fix it
or you could die.
[Gugu] I don't have time
for repairs right now!
Hurry up and pour it in me!
Hurry up!
[Rean's Mom] Come on,
Rean, we're leaving.
Huh?
Forget it!
I told you before,
I like it here!
[Rean's Mom] That's
quite enough, young lady.
You're just causing
trouble for these people.
She throws tantrums when
she doesn't get her way.
That's why she's left
home so many times.
But we're used to it now.
It's not really a
big problem for us.
So then you're saying
you really don't see a problem
with the way your
daughter behaves.
Come along, we're leaving.
No! I'm not going home!
It's not your decision to make.
-Stop it!
-I want to stay here!
Hmm?
[Gugu] She can't go
home now, not now.
That is not your decision
to make, now let go of me!
[Gugu] She can't go! I said no!
She's gotta stay here!
Just what is your
complaint with us, Rean?
Haven't we done everything
to make sure you become
a successful adult?
We've guided you
along all these years!
That's exactly it!
I want more freedom to grow up!
I want to make clumsy mistakes!
So clumsy that it
can be embarrassing.
(Dad groaning)
Alright, darling. I understand.
You didn't like that we chose
who you're going to
marry, that's it, right?
No! That's not it!
[Gugu] (laughing) Seriously?
You're telling me Rean already
has a husband lined up?
No, that's not exactly correct.
[Gugu] Well folks, I don't
know who that other guy is.
But I know that the guy
who loves Rean the most in
the entire world is me, Gugu!
Anyway, I gotta get going.
So deal with it!
Time for us to go home.
-(stick whooshes)
-(all gasping)
(Gugu panting)
[Gugu] Fushi! I made it back!
Where's the enemy?
Fushi?
Huh?
(monster roaring)
Oh, good, Fushi, you're safe!
Huh?
Wait a minute, that's not Fushi!
Fushi, where are you?
Fushi!
(dramatic music)
(monster roaring)
What did you do with
Fushi? You bastard!
Give Fushi back!
(monster roaring)
(Gugu groaning)
(Gugu screaming)
What do you think you're doing?
Out of our way!
(Gugu exhales)
Huh?
(dramatic music)
[Gugu] Here, have some more!
(Gugu shouts)
[Man] The forest, it's on fire!
Oh, Gugu...
[Gugu] Fushi, where did you go?
Are you broken?
I thought you were immortal.
(sobbing)
I was having so much
fun with you here.
For the first time in a long
time, I was actually happy.
You made me feel like
it was okay to be me.
Sorry, Fushi.
Sorry I turned out to be
such a useless brother.
(light whooshing)
Huh?
What the hell is that?
(soft music)
A rock?
[The Beholder] My goodness.
Fushi, aren't you the lucky one!
That being who holds
you in his hand,
who is brittle,
but in no way weak,
will make you even
stronger in time.
(music swells)
(magic whooshing)
[Gugu] Fushi!
Hey, I took the enemy down.
I'm not kidding!
Is that right?
[Gugu] Yeah!
Hey, that hurts, you ass!
(Gugu laughing)
Thank you so much, Gugu.
It's them! They're back!
Hey! So just what
happened out there?
[Gugu] Nothing at all!
(laughing) That's our Gugu!
Woo-hoo! I'm gonna
demolish this!
Oh my goodness, it's heaven!
Gugu always makes the best food!
Thanks so much for
coming back here, my boy!
Does this mean you've
decided to forgive me?
[Gugu] No, it doesn't.
What?!
[Gugu] I'm not calling
you Booze Man anymore.
From now on, you're gonna
be known as Booze Shithead!
However, you did save my life.
And because of that, I'm willing
to drop the shithead part
and just call you
Booze Man again.
Thanks so much, Gugu!
Hey! Watch your
mouth, young man.
Don't use that kind of
language with your elders.
[Gugu] Oh! Sorry, sir.
Um, you know something, dear?
This young man is
a pretty good cook.
Taste it, he's certainly
better than our chef.
Oh, my heavens!
Uh, hey, Gugu...
Do you know where Fushi went?
[Gugu] I asked him to go
out and get some water.
He should be back soon.
[The Beholder] Fushi, you
must leave this place.
Why is that?
[The Beholder] There is a way
for you to become stronger
as you face your challenges.
You should not stay in the
same spot for very long.
Really? I don't get it.
The Nokkers, as I've
decided to call them,
are a dangerous enemy.
Even as we speak,
they are hard at work,
plotting the destruction
of this world.
They learn from defeat.
They may have lost this time,
but they'll ensure
they win the next time.
In your current state,
you will surely lose.
They'll attack and take what
is inside you again and again,
and you will return to a
state of moss and rock.
You understand that, don't you?
Gugu will fight with me
and defeat the enemy.
Gugu is strong.
I need Gugu to help me.
So I will stay.
[The Beholder] That, of
course, is an option.
If you want to see how this
path ends, I won't stop you.
-[Gugu] Fushi.
-Huh?
[Gugu] What's going on?
You've been out here
talking to yourself.
That isn't like you.
So then you don't see?
[Gugu] See what?
Just get your butt
in here, will ya?
Everybody's already eating.
What?! You're going home?
Yes. I appreciate all
you've done for me.
[Gugu] Are you sure about this?
I mean, with your
parents and all.
Well, I can tell you
one thing for sure,
they're not going
to budge from here
until I agree to
go home with them.
Besides, I guess I've
just lost any interest
in that whole situation!
[Gugu] I guess I shouldn't
be all that surprised.
The two of us seem to
have one thing in common.
Huh?
[Gugu] The people
who keep us alive
don't necessarily have our
best interests at heart, but...
We're both strong
enough to endure it.
Mm-hm!
I'll be seeing you
again real soon Old Man,
Old Lady, Fushi,
and Mr. Shopboy!
[Gugu] Did you just
call me Shopboy?
Come on, Gugu, I'm kidding.
(Gugu gasping)
(Booze Man chuckles)
[Booze Man] Well, folks,
it's time to set up shop.
[Pioran] That's your job,
I'm going back to bed.
[Fushi] Uh, so, Gugu...
[Gugu] Yeah? What is it?
[Fushi] You need to teach me
how to cook as good as you.
[Gugu] Whoa, and just
where did that come from?
Do you suddenly
look up to me now?
[Older Gugu] Gentlemen, welcome.
[Man] You know, I'll have the
same thing I got last time.
[Man 2] Well in that case,
can I try a sip of that?
[Older Gugu] Of course.
[Man] The booze you guys
make is really gotten good!
[Older Gugu] Thanks very much.
You've worked at this place
for a while now, haven't you?
I bet you've been here for
at least the last four years.
Am I right?
[Older Gugu] Yep.
S'cuse me, Gugu, can you
give me a hand back here?
[Older Gugu] Why'd you
put this heavy jar on top?
Couldn't you have split
this up into two batches?
You've gotten pretty big and
strong, haven't you, kid?
Yeah, you were just
a little shrimp
when you first came around here.
[Older Gugu] How did
I end up being me?
I used to ask myself
that all the time.
The truth is, I really
hated myself back then.
And how do you feel
about yourself now, Gugu,
four years later?
Mm-hm!
Surprised to see me?
[Older Gugu] Uh, hey, Rean,
running away from home again?
Yep. The second time this month.
[Older Gugu] What's
your excuse this time?
I heard that Fushi's developed
an interest in needlework.
So I brought him a bunch
of materials from home.
[Older Gugu] He's in the
kitchen making lunch right now.
I'll go upstairs then.
My gosh, it looks so delicious!
He's gotten really good
at cooking, hasn't he?
[Older Gugu] Why don't
you stick around and eat?
Thanks.
[Older Gugu] Hm, that's
strange. I thought he'd be here.
If you're looking for
Fushi, he went to wash up.
[Older Gugu] Come on, old woman!
You can't just grab a chair
and start eating by yourself!
I keep telling you to wait
until everyone's at the table!
Oh, shut up!
The food's gonna get cold if I
wait around and don't eat it!
[Fushi] Hm?
Oh.
[Older Gugu] Hey,
Fushi, hurry up.
Everyone's eating already.
Yeah, in a second.
[Older Gugu] What were you
staring at for so long?
You ready to pop all those zits?
No. I noticed hair
growing on my chin.
[Older Gugu] What?
You're getting a beard?
[Fushi] Does this
mean I'm growing up?
[Older Gugu] Sure does.
Congratulations, Fushi.
(soft music)
(closing theme music)
Preview
[The Beholder] Four
years have passed
since the battle
with the Nokkers.
Our heroes have matured,
with no imminent threats.
But their peace
will be short-lived.
Gugu's lost older brother,
Shin, returns from the past
Gift From the Past