(opening theme music)
Here's how it works, you take
this and give it a good tug.
A good tug.
By the way, Fushi, I'm
turning 16 next month,
and my parents are
throwing a big party
to mark the occasion.
Would you and Gugu
both like to come?
Yeah, sure. I'll let
Gugu know about it.
I'm so happy!
[The Beholder] Four
years have passed,
and in all that time,
Fushi has not physically
transformed himself even once.
And since he never regenerated
by the process of
changing forms,
his body has aged in accordance
with the time that has passed.
There are two reasons
Fushi hasn't changed forms.
The first is that
he's been fortunate
not to encounter his
archenemy, the Nokkers, again.
The second is that Fushi himself
has consciously chosen
not to transform.
He wants to experience
life the same way
Gugu and the others do.
And so, as a result, he hasn't
created anything, either.
In my opinion, life as a
human being is a repetition
of mundane events
lacking in stimulation.
With little to risk,
there is little to gain.
A typical day might expose
Fushi to a crayfish,
a thread shrimp, a
wet cloth and bucket,
Meer the dog, a pot,
a stone weight, pottery shards,
a nasty potato, and
a sewing needle.
-(needle thuds)
-(Fushi groans)
Oh, dear! Did you poke yourself?
I'll ask the old man
for some disinfectant.
Don't do that.
I'm fine. It's not a big deal.
Are you sure?
Oh, yeah.
Remind me, what were
we talking about?
Um, you were describing some
of the things Gugu likes.
Right. I know one thing he
likes for sure is crayfish.
Interesting.
All right, then on the day of
the party, I'll cook some up.
Yep. I've been wanting
to give him something.
If I made him a shirt,
-do you think he'd wear it?
-I'm not sure.
I've never seen him wear one.
He's a tough nut.
I wonder if there's anything
I could make that he'd want.
Well, I heard him say he wanted
a rag for his feet,
the other day.
A rag? I don't really think so.
Come on. You know
Gugu as well as I do.
I'm sure he'd appreciate
anything at all.
Hm. I hope you're right.
Gift From the Past
You probably don't
understand this,
but I have to get married
right after I turn 16,
to someone my
parents have chosen.
Do you know that word? Married?
Uh-uh.
It's awful. Just the worst.
It means that, in the end,
I have to become
just like my mother.
I get together with
a person I don't love
and give birth to
some snotty brat.
You don't want that?
Well, of course not.
The fact of the matter is,
I've never even really
seen this guy's face.
Oh, yeah? Does he wear
a mask, like Gugu does?
No, you misunderstand
what I mean.
Listen, first of all,
I refuse to marry
someone I don't like.
So to avoid that situation,
I'm thinking of
introducing my boyfriend
to Mom and Dad at
the birthday party.
That means before that,
I'm really gonna need
to find a boyfriend,
which means I'm
gonna need to become
close with someone I like.
Becoming close is kinda hard,
but I have to make it work.
That thing you just said
is like how it sounds
when Gugu talks about you.
-Huh?
-So I wonder,
is this thing you're feeling-
Gugu's been talking about
me? What's he been saying?
And does that mean your
secret boyfriend is-
Look, it's done! I created
a crayfish face mask!
What do you think?!
That looks great. You
giving it to Gugu?
[Rean] Maybe. What did you make?
A sweat rag for Booze
Man, for his pits.
(Rean laughs)
-Very good job!
-(Rean clapping)
Now that I think about
it, it's the perfect gift.
He will love it.
Gugu?
It is you, right?
It's Shin, your brother.
[Fushi] You gonna ask him?
[Rean] Huh?
Gugu, I mean.
Ask him what?
To marry you, of course.
Now what makes you think
we were talking about Gugu?
Sorry, I thought
that was obvious.
You must know by now, right?
Gugu is just crazy about you.
So if you need to
find a boyfriend,
I'm sure he'd be
glad to marry you.
(Booze Man groans)
-Oh, man, am I beat.
-Hey, welcome home, old man.
I have a gift for you.
Huh? What in the world's that?
Well, I'll be darned, a sweat
rag for my pits! Thanks!
-What a thoughtful idea.
-I'm gonna go give
my gift too.
[Fushi] Right.
Just give it to him later.
He's kinda busy right now.
It's been a while, huh?
How have you been doing?
You've changed a lot since
the last time I saw you.
What's with that helmet?
Are you hiding your face?
I heard you've been
living here for a while.
How is it?
I mean, are you enjoying it?
So, you look well.
And hey, if you're happy,
then I'm glad for you.
Getting away from me?
I guess that was
kind of a good thing.
[Gugu] Why are you here, Shin?
You wanna tell tell me what
a piece of trash you are?!
Huh? What's happening, old man?
Gugu's older brother
just showed up.
I'm sorry, Gugu. I really am.
I don't know what was
wrong with me back then.
[Gugu] You think it's
something fixable?
You haven't got a clue, Shin!
That's who you really are!
You betrayed and abandoned
your kid brother!
You're angry. And you
have every right to be.
Even so, you gave me this
when I didn't deserve it.
(Gugu gasps)
You gave me everything
you could give.
(hand slaps)
I'm sorry, Gugu. It took
me four years to find you.
I've reformed. I work
selling farm tools now.
I just hired some people,
and things are finally
stable in my life.
I eat properly every day.
And even though our dream
of building a mansion is a
ways off, it's still possible,
and I wanna realize
that dream with you.
I wanna make things
right with you, Gugu.
And I want to start over.
You and I, together
again, as brothers.
Will you come with me?
(Rean gasps)
[Gugu] I'm gonna pass.
After you abandoned me,
I was truly miserable,
but I survived.
And what I gained was something
I could never have hoped for.
It was practically a miracle.
Booze Man, the unhinged
genius who saved my life;
Pioran, a grandma
filled with knowledge;
the always kind Rean, who
visits us now and then;
and Fushi, who's like
a younger brother,
and irreplaceable to me.
I treasure all of them,
so please, don't take
anything else away from me.
Sure. I understand.
[Gugu] Well, I have work to do.
If you ever need any help,
you can always count
on your big brother.
I know you have no reason
to believe me, Gugu,
but it's the only
thing I can think to do
to prove that I am
your big brother.
(bird chirping)
Hi! You wanna come in?
Oh, that was fast. Are
you done talking already?
I'm sorry for barging in on you,
but there's something I
need to give back to Gugu.
I wonder, could you help me
out and pass this along to him?
[Booze Man] Hm. All right.
Thank you so much.
Goodbye.
-So what is it?
-Huh.
What the heck did he give you?
(Rean gasp)
-Hm?
-This ring.
What do you think?
Isn't that ring just
perfect for you, darling?
You know, I had a craftsman
make it up special.
Yuck. This color is awful.
Rean, are you okay?
(Rean gasps)
(gentle music)
I have fresh produce here!
Come and get your
fresh vegetables!
I've seen that boy before.
He's here every day.
You're right about that, miss.
He must be helping his family.
But isn't it weird that he's
working? He's just a kid.
That's sad.
Not at all. I think it's
quite admirable of him.
Oh, no! Meer has run
away from home again!
I have to find him!
Meer! Meer!
Huh?
I have to find a
way to thank him.
Now I know. Now I
know that was you.
You all right, young lady?
Mm-hm. My mind was wandering.
Hey, is it okay if
I give this to Gugu?
[Booze Man] Sure. Thanks a lot.
Hey, Gugu! Gugu!
(Gugu snoring)
Sleeping.
(Rean grunting)
-(Gugu gasping)
-(Rean gasps)
[Gugu] Rean!
What are you doing to me?!
So, Gugu, now is your
chance to make a move on me.
[Gugu] What?!
I mean, are you saying...
Why would...
Hm?
Because I'm gonna be forced
to get married soon, you dummy!
[Gugu] What?! You are?!
Just tell me this, then,
are you okay with me getting
married to someone else?
[Gugu] What?!
What's up with you?!
Why would you ask me that?!
Oh, stop it! You do
love me, don't you?!
[Gugu] Huh?! What are
you talking about?!
Don't tell me you've
forgotten already!
My parents were there!
That day you came back
after running away,
you said you were the one
who loved me the most!
[Gugu] How embarrassing!
I really said that?!
I don't recall saying that.
(Rean gasps)
-(Rean grunting)
-(potatoes clattering)
My birthday party's
happening next month,
and you'd better be there
with a gift, mister!
[Gugu] Huh?
(steam hisses)
What in the heck happened here?
You just paid your
dues for the booze.
The truth is, alcohol
makes you forget things.
It erases them from your memory.
You messed up big time, Gugu.
But forget about
that! I have news!
[Gugu] Huh?
I've finally completed it!
Presenting the all new
Anti-Tree Man mask!
[Gugu] Tree Man?
You know, the thing that
attacked you a few years ago.
I don't remember
all the details.
[Gugu] You mean you made
me this because of that?
Yeah, took a whole year
and a bunch of parts.
Go ahead, kiddo, try it on.
[Gugu] Whoa!
It's a bit heavy,
but it's functional.
It can even make fire
without a live torch.
Watch what happens when you
close the lid real fast.
There's a ball of tinder
at the tip of the nose
that catches fire
from the pressure.
-(fire roars)
-(Gugu grunts)
[Gugu] This is great,
Booze Man! Awesome!
[Booze Man] I'm sure Rean
will be impressed as well.
If you wear it to her party,
you're gonna get her full
attention, believe me!
-(Booze Man laughs)
-Thank you!
Okay, all set.
Let's go, Fushi!
We're gonna be late for
Rean's birthday party!
So, Gugu, before you go,
why don't you empty the
liquor in your belly?
I'm sure you'll need space
for all that good grub.
[Gugu] Nah, it's fine.
After all, there's no telling
when the enemy will attack.
I wanna be ready for
anything that happens.
Okay, we'll see you.
Hang on, Gugu.
[Gugu] Hm?
I just wanna say, you
sure are a good kid.
We aren't related,
but I really do think
of you as my grandson.
[Gugu] What brought that
on? You're creeping me out.
[Booze Man] Sorry
about that, kid.
You boys have a good time.
[Gugu] Okay. See you
when we get back.
[Fushi] Does this map
look upside-down to you?
(Booze Man sobbing)
Hey, what are you sobbing for?
He's only gonna be
away until tomorrow.
That isn't what
started the waterworks.
I'm not upset about that.
It's about how time passes so
quickly. It suddenly hit me.
I mean, how in the hell did
I get to be such an old fart?
I can't stand the thought that
I'm going to die before him,
and probably miss everything.
He's had such a tough
road to get to this point.
I want him to move out
on his own, grow up,
choose his own path, and
become whatever he wants.
That's the kinda normal
life I want him to have.
And I don't wanna die
until after I get to
see all that happen.
(people chattering)
[Gugu] What have
you got in the bag?
A bunch of veggies.
Pioran said it's not
polite to go to a wedding
without bringing a nice gift.
So what did you finally
decide to bring?
[Gugu] I'm gonna buy
something here at the market.
There, that's it!
It's perfect! Hello.
Welcome, I...
Welcome, sir.
[Gugu] I'd like one of those
purple flowers, please.
A flower?
[Gugu] I went over
it in my mind.
It's about the only
thing I can think of
that Rean might like.
This blossom is called the
dream bellflower, my friend.
[Gugu] Yeah.
This must be the place!
I had no idea she
lived like this.
This place is almost
as big as our village.
The floor's so shiny.
Check out that
yummy-looking food!
Let me get a plate for you.
What should I grab
first? Oh, spring rolls.
You like pork, don't you?
They have noodles too.
Grape juice to drink,
-and pear jelly for dessert.
-Hm?
What's up with that guy?
Why the mask? This isn't
supposed to be a costume party.
How does someone like
that even know Rean?
[Gugu] Rean sure has
a lot of friends.
There must be more than
a hundred of them here.
And yet Rean is the only
friend we have, isn't she?
Hello, there. This
is quite an honor.
Rean, hello.
-Huh?!
-Thanks for coming today,
both of you.
Hey, look, bet you didn't
expect to see this.
The old man made
Gugu a new mask.
He did a great job.
It's really beautiful.
Oh.
[Gugu] Um, hey,
Rean, I wanted to...
Do you mind if I ask you
something about the other day?
Oh, sure! Which day?
And by the way, I'm
sorry for throwing
those potatoes at you.
Potatoes?
What happened that day?
Did I accidentally
break your mask?
Is that why you had
to get a new one?
I'm sorry about that, really.
[Gugu] Actually,
that's not why I got-
What do you have in
the basket, Fushi?
They look great! Are
these gifts for me?
Yup. They're veggies.
Thank you so much!
Gugu, give her yours.
[Gugu] Here. Happy
16th birthday, Rean.
[Boy] Isn't that the
same flower that-
[Boy] Yeah. What does
he think he's doing?
So, Gugu, why did you choose
this particular flower?
[Gugu] Uh, no real reason.
I just thought you might
like the petals on this one,
since they're purple.
How insensitive are you?
That's the kind of
flower she was holding
when she was injured
four years ago.
You'd have to be an idiot
to think that would
be a nice present.
[Gugu] I'm so sorry, Rean!
I didn't have any idea!
Don't worry, it's fine. You
two have fun at the party.
[Gugu] Oh, no, I blew it, Fushi!
At least you didn't
bring potatoes.
(people chattering)
[Rean] Oh, these
flowers are so pretty.
I wonder what they're called.
I would love to have
a dress in this color.
(Rean gasps)
That was the first time I'd
ever seen a flower like this.
I've never seen
another one since then.
-Rean, give me that flower.
-(Rean gasps)
I'll throw it out. It
will just make you sad.
No, Mother. Doesn't matter.
It's the first time he
ever gave me anything.
[Boy] Hey, Mr. Party Poop.
I'm talking to you, mister,
the one with the mask.
[Gugu] Huh?
I've had my eye
on you ever since
you walked through
the front door.
This is a celebration.
Take that thing off.
[Gugu] Believe me,
I know. But I can't.
What do you mean, you can't?!
[Gugu] Wait!
[Boy] You look
dumb in this thing!
(both grunting)
-(foot thuds)
-(Gugu gasps)
-(water splashes)
-(people gasping)
(Rean gasps)
(people chattering)
[Rean] What's going on?!
[Boy] This guy tripped and
fell right in the water.
Can somebody please
give me towel? Here.
You're going to get
all wet, young lady.
Come on now, dry your
face off with this.
Oh, that's right, you
won't take that off.
But really, Gugu,
with that thing on,
you'll never be able
to kiss anybody.
(people laughing)
(people chattering)
That's enough now.
Come along, your
father's calling for you.
Sure! Get all dried off, Gugu,
so you don't catch a cold!
Rean! Come over here, please.
I wanna introduce you
to your betrothed.
Nice to finally meet you, Rean.
You have big eyes.
You're very cute.
[Fushi] Mm mm mm.
[Gugu] Okay, Fushi,
time to head home.
Wait. Why leave now?
I'm still eating.
[Gugu] Listen to me, Fushi,
I thought Rean was always
gonna be part of our lives.
I never imagined she'd ever
stop coming to visit us.
But the truth is, it's
not gonna be that way.
No? Why?
[Gugu] Just because,
because those are the rules.
Well, who decided that?
Your life isn't something
that's given to you!
You have to earn it
for yourself, Gugu!
[Gugu] Hold on. Is that a
thought you made up on your own?
-Not really.
-(Gugu groans)
[Gugu] Go eat. I'll
be waiting outside.
-(water running)
-(bird squawking)
-(footsteps pattering)
-Gugu!
-Huh?
-(Rean panting)
You're leaving already?
Are you upset about what
happened in there earlier?
[Gugu] No. I'm used to it.
(birds squawking)
There's something
that's not clear to me.
You might not like this,
but may I ask you again,
about your mask and your injury?
Oh, and don't worry,
I promise I won't hate you,
no matter what you say.
[Gugu] I fell from a
pretty steep cliff.
According to Booze
Man, when he found me,
there was a log
resting on my head.
That's how my face
got smashed in.
How did you fall off the cliff?
[Gugu] I'd seen the log
rolling down a hill.
Then, I saw it was
going to hit someone.
I shouted, but they
didn't hear me,
so I ran to try and help them.
I did what I could,
but I screwed up.
I don't understand why
you hid this from me.
It was such a noble thing to do.
[Gugu] No, it wasn't, because
I screwed up really badly.
What happened? Did that
person not make it?
[Gugu] No, they survived.
But they ended up with an
injury anyway, about this big.
That's ridiculous!
It's only a scratch compared
to the injury you suffered!
[Gugu] The actual
size didn't matter.
To her, it was a huge injury.
It really bothered her.
She was too embarrassed
to let anyone see it.
I felt bad because I
knew I had caused it.
You saved that girl's life.
I bet I know exactly
what happened.
(leaves rustling)
Want me to take a guess, Gugu?
It was probably windy
that day, right?
[Gugu] Yeah.
It was a lovely place,
right along the river.
It was around sunset. All
the flowers were in bloom.
[Gugu] Yeah.
They were purple flowers.
She had just picked
some of them.
[Gugu] That's right.
I heard that they're
called dream bellflowers.
Gugu, there's so much
I need to say to you.
(floor cracks)
(floor breaks)
(Rean gasps)
Gugu!