(thunder rumbling
and rain pouring)
How did I end up being me?
No matter how much I wanted
to I couldn't do anything.
I'm so sorry, Gugu.
It's too late to apologize now.
(opening theme music)
[The Beholder] It's been
four and a half days
since Fushi left
Booze Man's home.
In that time he's
walked alone in silence.
Many different expressions
have crossed his face.
It's obvious he's
in great turmoil
as he desperately tries
to process his emotions.
With Gugu's death,
he seems to have acquired
something invisible.
Hey. Come out, black thing.
I presume, by "black
thing" you mean me.
What is it?
This is the first time
you've ever called for me.
Aspiring to Go Higher
So now what is it
I'm supposed to do?
Continue moving forward.
Become stronger,
so that you can
take back the piece
that was stolen from you.
Tell me truthfully, what am I?
What is it that you
really want from me?
The answer is the same
as I have said before.
You are a mechanism for
collecting and preserving
the information of this land.
It was I who created you.
I am effectively your parent.
You're wrong.
You are not my parent.
My parent was...
Um...
Is something the matter?
Why am I the only one
who's always left alive?
Why did Gugu, why
did Gugu have to die?
It's simply a
difference in nature.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
That's because it's too
early for you to understand.
However, I am gratified that
you're able to question things,
-as that will-
-Don't insult me!
Tell me the truth!
Everything perishes.
That's why you're needed.
You're a special
entity in this world,
one that rises above
the natural order.
For that reason the enemies,
the Nokkers, seem to
want to control you.
In that case will the Nokkers
stop coming if I'm not me?
Interesting idea.
I'll try it.
(Fushi hissing angrily)
Taking on that form
doesn't constitute
having abandoned yourself.
If the Nokkers come while
you're in that configuration,
they'll simply have
their way with you.
If you continue to
confront them and lose,
you'll regress to
a state of nothing
back to the orb.
And you'll never return
to what you are now.
You won't be able to.
I wouldn't mind if
that happened,
but I'm sure you would.
If it's so important
then why don't you fight
against them too?
Obviously you can control
me, so give me more strength.
Yes, that would
indeed be simple.
But even if I could
control your body,
I can't control your mind.
The Nokkers, they
are relentless.
Until their objective of
killing us is put to an end,
the attacks will continue.
You may not believe this,
but it will be you not me
who ultimately stops them.
One day I will no
longer be here.
You need to begin preparing
now to defeat them
on your own when
that time comes.
You are a critical step
in achieving my goal of-
I don't care!
It's not my problem!
(Fushi groans)
Oh my word.
You've grown to be quite
a troublesome, young man.
Damn it!
Nothing is going to
bring Gugu back to life.
So I don't care anymore.
I have no interest in what
happens to me or anyone.
Really? Are you sure about that?
(wind blowing)
This scent, why is it here?
(Pioran squeals)
Pioran?
Hi!
I suddenly realized something.
When we first got together,
I came to Takunaha
hoping I could help you.
But in the end I discovered I
couldn't do anything for you.
Then you left.
So I thought I'd
give it another try.
Yes. I get that.
But who will take
care of the old man?
Don't worry.
I told them all about
what I was going to do.
Rean and Shin jumped
right in and said
they'd keep the
business going for us.
And besides, Rean
figured out what happened
with you and Gugu back there.
I think that's why she
decided to let me leave,
and come find you.
Pioran, go home.
What? How dare you?
You're gonna turn down
an innocent old
lady's offer to help?
You know the kind of
trouble I attract.
It's dangerous.
I've thought the
whole thing through.
The question is, how do I give
meaning to what little time
I have left in this life?
I'll be your walking stick.
Even if I turn out to
be an inch-long twig.
That is my wish.
I'm dragging you home!
They need you at home,
I have to take you back!
(both panting heavily)
Why won't you listen to me?
I can't deal with this.
I don't want anyone to cry
because someone
close to them died,
I can't see that anymore.
So will you please go home!
Go home for my sake!
Shut up, you immortal freak!
It's my life! Let
me do as I please!
(Fushi groans)
(Pioran exhales heavily)
Fine. Suit yourself.
(rain pouring)
Here, have a potato.
Don't want it.
-Here, have some tea.
-Don't want it.
Here, have some fish.
I said I don't want it!
Here you go, you must be cold.
(Fushi exhales loudly)
Listen, Pioran,
promise me something.
What's that?
Don't die on me.
Right.
Well look there. It's a town.
I'm starving to death.
This seems like a good
time to take a break!
Hyaaa!
Pioran!
(Pioran slurping)
Pioran, can we go already?
[Shopkeeper] Welcome!
I haven't had a meal
like this in ages!
It's delicious!
I'm telling you, if those
things show up look out.
I won't be able to
protect the town.
Fine. Just give me a second.
Hey, man! You got
any kind of booze?
[Shopkeeper] Coming up!
Pioran!
So, where are the
Nokkers at this moment?
Six kilometers
northwest of here.
I haven't sensed it move
for the past four days,
since it burrowed into the soil.
Did you say sensed?
Are you saying you always
know where they are?
They're like insects
crawling over your body.
You don't notice them
when they're small eggs,
but once they hatch and
start to move around
they cause intense discomfort.
Hm? Can't you explain in
a way I can understand?
Who are you talking to?
Uh. No one.
Hey, here's your food.
Fushi.
Huh?
Tell me what's going on.
You say this man
is all in black,
and he's telling you you
have to become stronger.
That it's the only way you
can overcome the Nokkers?
Yeah.
So, tell me what you
want to do about it.
Huh?
I don't wanna do
just as he says.
But if the Nokkers do show up
I'm the only one who would
have a fighting chance
to protect Pioran.
That man in black is right.
I can't defeat them as I am now.
So I have no choice.
I have to become stronger.
That bastard!
He made me come across Pioran,
knowing this would happen to me!
So, listen, the truth is I
don't expect you to protect me.
Huh?
I have to say, living
on the edge of danger
each day can appealing.
You know?
Yeah.
Is living like that
really good enough?
I feel like I've
forgotten something.
Oh, that fruit looks
absolutely delicious!
Climb up there and grab
some for me, will you?
Oh, I don't have to do that.
You see?
Absolutely gross!
I'm not eating that!
Forget about it!
Fine, whatever.
What the...
Well that was pathetic.
What's wrong with you?
Just take on March's form again.
How hard can it be?
Who's March?
What? March, you fool!
You know who I mean!
She was the tiny one!
Who're you talking about?
Oh come on, kid, you've changed
into her dozens of times!
Concentrate! Don't you dare
tell me you've forgotten her!
Aww!
I'm remembering.
I can see my self being
able to climb trees.
Fushi, you go first!
Fushi, make me a stick!
I do remember.
You were robbed. The
Nokkers took March from you.
Someone was kind to me,
and gave me many things.
Open your mouth
and say thank you.
Here you really funny puppy!
Becoming a grown-up means you
get to know everything, right?
Is that...
Is that March's voice I hear?
That's right. She was really
important to me, wasn't she?
You finally understand.
It's not your fault.
You can't be expected
to recall something
once you've lost it.
I see how it works.
When the enemy attacks it
takes your memories as well.
If it was able to kill you
while you happened
to be in Gugu's form
then you'd lose all
memories of him as well.
Yeah.
Fact is it's actually
like a second death.
Huh!
The way I see it
Rean and Booze Man,
Parona of Ninannah, and me too,
we'll all die.
But we'll only be truly dead
once we've been forgotten.
I won't let that happen.
I'll get much stronger.
Now that I've made up my mind
I have to figure this out.
Even if I'm playing right
into the black thing's hands.
[Gugu] From what I've seen,
you can make new things in
reaction to physical pain.
I mean, that's how
it works, right?
All I have to do is
stimulate myself with pain.
It's easy.
But I can't turn
myself into a rock.
I'll lose awareness, and
that won't help anybody.
The problem is that as
far as living things go,
I can't transform while
the subject is still alive.
That's a nasty thought.
Ohh look, a crab flower!
These things are really sweet!
The eyes are made of bugs
so we don't eat them.
The flower is delicious,
so we'll make salad
out of that later.
And then we boil it live
with plenty of salt!
What's wrong, Fushi?
When I'm near something
I feel what it feels.
You know, pain and suffering,
and stuff like that.
Wow! That's uncomfortable.
Has it always been like that?
Yeah. That's why I
always had Gugu step in.
He'd cut up the seafood before
we cooked it for dinner.
I didn't know.
Here you go. Try this.
-Yummy!
-Yeah, it's good.
I don't have the guts
to become a crab yet.
So far all I can make
so far is a corpse.
I guess I could
probably make Gugu, too.
If anyone wanted a
limp, motionless Gugu.
So Fushi, talk to me,
how did you defeat the Nokkers
the last time you
engaged them in battle?
Huh?
Well, to tell you the truth
I'm not absolutely sure.
Gugu blew fire on it which
made it jump into the water,
and that's where the rocks
on its body fell apart.
That explains it!
Heated stone becomes brittle
when it cools down too fast!
(Fushi gasps)
You're right, that
worked really well.
But I don't know
about the next time.
I mean if it shakes
me off I'll die.
Yeah, and the fact is,
you can't count on there
being water nearby.
You're going to have to
learn to be versatile
when you fight.
Wait, I've got it!
I know a place that's
perfect, Fushi!
I just remembered,
there's a ship that goes to
Sarlnine from the port up ahead.
It's been there forever.
It's an animal paradise.
The best part is,
nobody comes near it.
You can train all that you like,
no one will bother you.
But a ship, that would be
dangerous if the Nokkers came.
Come on, it's not
that much of a risk!
You're gonna be trapped forever
if you keep imagining the
worst possible scenario.
Alright, let's do it.
This is the ship that's
going to transport us.
I'm sorry ma'am, you're late.
This ship is completely full.
Allow me to show you to
that ship over there.
This way, please.
I'll take care of
the donkey for you.
Thanks, young lady.
(Pioran yawns)
I'm gonna take a nap.
All women passengers
have to come with me.
What? Is that some
kind of a rule?
This area is quite
dangerous. Sorry.
Well then, Fushi, I'll
see you when we get there.
-Right.
-Bye.
Come along, sir, you're
with me. Right over here.
In you go!
Huh?
It's time to give each
of you your tickets!
Please put out your hands!
[Prisoner] I never
agreed to this.
Next!
You.
(Fushi groaning)
[Sailor] Next!
Next!
Pioran!
I'm here to welcome
you, prisoners!
Starting today you're
all part of a family!
You're being transported
to the one place
that will accept trash like you.
Enjoy the voyage
because once you arrive,
it will be the last
place you will ever see.
Prepare to experience heaven
or as close as you'll ever get,
Jananda Island!
What have we gotten
ourselves into?
And where's Pioran?
You there, hold it.
What's happened
to your shackles?
Huh?
That's odd. Your brand
is missing as well.
Did you get on board the ship
with the other
prisoners by mistake?
I'm sorry, boss! It's my fault!
-Huh?
-I made a mistake.
Hm?
I see. For crying out loud,
be more careful from now on!
Trust is important
to our business.
Yes sir! I'll take him back.
This way, come on.
Where is Pioran? The
woman who was with me?
I don't know. She's probably
been taken in by now.
Huh?
Don't worry.
Everyone who comes
here eventually learns
to accept it and smile.
The thing is I've
never understood why.
Is it because they're
actually happy here?
Or because if they don't
act happy they'll go crazy?
Hold on. You can't just
wander off down here!
Oh boy.
What a pain.
She's in there.
Where's the entrance? I can't
find it. Nothing's marked.
I can't dig through this stone.
I wonder if I can make
my way up the side?
(Fushi groans)
(Fushi gasps)
(Sandel gasp)
Don't look!
It's you!
Did you see that?
I did!
Me too! Cool beans!
Um, are we supposed
to keep it secret?
That bow of yours give it.
Uh, here.
Wait a minute. How do
you use this again?
Ah!
That's right. Now I remember.
If I can become that bird I
can make it over the wall.
I don't have a choice.
Alright-
Not alright!
(Fushi groans)
What did you do that for?
Your target happens
to be my partner.
I mean, I couldn't
just let you shoot him.
Yeah. Give the bow back.
You can't just walk away!
If you don't know how
things work around here
you'll get in trouble real fast!
Fine, so why don't you tell me.
How do I get over that wall?
-Um, I don't know.
-Same here.
I'm no help.
You're looking for your
friend Pioran, is that right?
I'm sad to say that's a problem.
Even if you find her she'll
never be able to leave here.
Huh?
This is the last stop
for these people.
Violent, incorrigible murderers
are brought from all over
to be kept on this
island forever.
It's escape-proof.
Once you become a prisoner
here there's no getting out.
Do you remember when
they branded your hand?
That thing marks
you as a prisoner.
She'll be a prisoner you know
for as long as she
has that mark on her.
This is horrible! It's your
fault! You brought us here!
Yeah, my bad. I
got that all wrong.
I made an honest mistake.
You're full of shit!
That was no mistake!
Well, lemme make
it up to you then.
If the two of you wanna escape
there's only one possible avenue
that offers you a way out.
This is it.
You have to win against all
opponents in this arena!
(closing theme music)
Preview
Jananda, known as the
island of the lawless.
An island where
prisoners kill each other
to try to have their
wishes granted.
Being immortal, and
unable to be killed,
Jananda, Island of Freedom