[The Beholder] Fushi
left behind the home
he had grown up in with Gugu,
who, for all practical
purposes, was his brother.
He found himself traveling again
with the old woman, Pioran,
as they set off to
a strange island.
But they fell into a trap
and were sent to a
prison island instead.
Once there, separated from
Pioran, Fushi was forced
to act on his own.
Alone and confused, he
tried to find his way.
He was like an
arrow without a bow.
(opening theme music)
[Receptionist] Group One
will begin immediately.
Line up over there if you're
participating in the arena.
Look at all the
people who came out.
No surprise there.
This tournament is the
biggest event on the island.
They all want to know one thing,
who's going to win?
If you pull it off,
you've hit the jackpot
and win entry to
everything on the island.
You can go anywhere and
do whatever you want.
If you felt like it, you could
proclaim yourself the king
and take the captured princess.
You could even leave the
island if you wanted.
What do you say?
Try it. What have
you got to lose?
All right.
I'll do it. It might
allow me to save Pioran.
Now you're talking
like a winner!
Well good luck, break a leg!
Oh wait, I forgot to ask.
What is it I have to do
to win the tournament?
Jananda, Island of Freedom
(suspenseful music)
So, what is it we have
to do in the arena?
(growls)
[Announcer] Let's
hear it, folks.
How are you all doing today?
It's been three days
since the previous
island chief passed away.
We hereby begin the 5,000th
competition for a new leader!
All the rules will remain
the same as before.
For the preliminaries,
there'll be eight
groups of contestants.
The eight men left
standing after that round
will then fight each other
in one-on-one battle.
(crowd cheering)
Contestants may use
any weapon they like.
The last one standing
is the winner.
(gasps)
You mean, all I have
to do is not die?
I can win!
Open the gates!
Group one, you may now enter--
(gates opening)
(men clamoring)
Begin the fight!
(men grunting in pain)
(steel clanking)
(vomits)
We know who's moving
ahead in this group.
Hold it! Not so fast,
there's still
someone left alive.
(crowd murmuring)
(heavy breathing)
Huh? Must've missed you
in all the confusion.
Bulls eye!
(crowd cheering)
(grunting)
What do I do now?
Everyone's watching.
They're going to see
that I can't be killed.
So Fushi, you need to
hide your abilities
when you're around other people.
If you're exposed, I'm sure
countries will go to war
to exploit you as a weapon.
What should I do?
Fall over?
But I can't win if I do that.
No, I don't have
time to worry about
what people are going to think.
Or even about what's
going to happen to me.
They'll just have
to deal with it.
(grunts)
(crowd confused)
In the end, that's why you
were able to protect Rean.
Isn't that right, Gugu?
Huh?
(gasping)
What the hell's going on here?
(groans)
Crap, I feel like shit.
I just remembered
I'm still drunk.
[Spectator] Are you kidding?
After he took out
everybody else?
[Spectator] You pathetic loser!
(crowd cheering)
Good job, buddy.
That was really amazing.
You took me totally by surprise.
I was like, "Whoa!"
Sorry, who are you?
The name's Tonari.
Nice to meet you.
[Local] I've never seen
anything like that.
What's up with your body?
[Female Local] Here, eat this.
It's all I have but I
want you to have it.
[Female Local] You
can have mine too.
Here. Oh, and I love your hair.
Hi, tell me something.
You think my child's cute?
Huh?
Sure?
Terrific!
So how about marrying me?
(instrument playing)
We've got a special
offer, folks!
If you want to talk to this boy,
pay two silver coins
and get in line.
Just for the first 100 people.
Line up, don't get left out.
Hold on there, you brats!
Why do you get to make all
the money off this kid?
Here's the deal,
Tonari found the guy.
Like it or not,
he belongs to her.
If you defy her, I'll use
a deadly poison next time.
All right, call out your
names one at a time.
Excuse me, what
are you guys doing?
It's simple, dude.
Everyone wants to
get close to you.
Chances are, you're probably
the next island chief.
It's understandable,
they all want their
wishes granted
when you win the tournament.
You know, like leaving
the island for example.
Until now, no one's
lasted very long.
None of the island chiefs
have lived more than 2 weeks.
But this time is
really different.
I mean, you're immortal!
They want to get
on your good side
so they can win your favor
when you take over everything.
That's what that huge
line is all about.
Yeah?
Our job is to simply
broker your services
for a small 80% commission.
Don't thank me.
I don't understand.
Tonari, what the hell is this?
I thought I told you to
take this boy back to town.
Why is he competing
in the tournament?
Hey boss, you're
timing is perfect.
I want you to go and
prepare lots of ships.
Huh?
We can finally band together
and leave this island.
Those of us who aren't criminals
will be able to go
live normal lives.
What do you think the captain's
going to say about this?
I hate to burst your
bubble but he'll murder us!
The reason this
island's so dangerous
is because there's no
one around to manage it.
But now, I found an
answer to that problem.
This is someone who could
become an eternal leader.
The truth is, I won't
need the ships right away.
But please, just bear with me,
let me watch over him.
Until I'm sure
everything's ready.
Fine, but be careful.
Huh?
Hey, where are you going?
You're just asking
to get messed up
wondering around
town on your own.
(footsteps)
Remember, my name's Uroy.
My favorite food
is fried chicken.
My name is Mia.
My favorite hobby is
collecting curly black hair.
Hey, I'm Sandel and
I'm 11 years old.
This one is Oopa.
This is Ligard, he's
a three-toed owl.
What do you want?
Why are you all following me?
You must be bored, right?
Why don't you let
us show you around?
The middle of this city is
where the arena is located.
The outer rim of the settlement
is surround by three churches.
The Church of Bennett is
where we were earlier.
To the north is the
Church of Monjo.
And to the west is
the Church of Zumla.
Between the churches
and the arena,
it's mostly houses.
We figured that they're
probably keeping the churches
to impress outsiders.
To say the rule of
law is being upheld,
and the religions are
also keeping a close eye
on all the prisoners.
Yeah.
This, of course, is
the farming district.
We keep animals here too.
In fact, we're fully
self sufficient.
(gasps)
Hey!
What's all this about?
Oh, I guess they must've
stolen some food or something.
If you have good reason,
you're allow to
kill people here.
It's the right that's
needed to keep the peace.
You see this kind of
thing all the time.
I'm telling you, you
better get used to it.
That's right.
It's horrible, I don't know how
you can stand to live here.
Well, there are some
people who do leave.
But there are only so many ships
and resources to go around.
People get pretty angry
when they come up short.
We keep an eye on each other,
it's every man for himself.
Traitors don't last very long,
they're killed as soon
as they're caught.
In our case,
we put up with this place
as patiently as possible
while we wait for a chance
to get out of here alive.
It's always been a prison.
It used to belong to some nation
that banished its very worst
criminals here for life.
But they sent so many convicts
that in the end, they couldn't
keep it under control.
Eventually,
there were non prisoners
left to run the island,
so the inmates made a deal to
operate this place themselves.
One of the operating
task we've been given
is to cross the water to
bring in more prisoners.
It's a job that's given
to the small hand full
of people around here
who aren't inmates.
And as you've observed,
I'm one of them of course.
Really?
(startled)
Oh, you mean, this?
This is the mark you receive
if you happen to be the
family member of a prisoner.
The ones for actual prisoners
have a circle in the middle.
(footstep)
Wait, you mean some prisoners
around this place
live normal lives?
Of course!
When we first met,
didn't you tell me
that Pioran was being
held as a prisoner?
Maybe.
Did I?
You think I'm a fool?
Why is Pioran still in custody?
Why hasn't she been released?
You better start
telling me the truth,
who told you to bring us here?
I imagine she's being
held in isolation.
She is a violent
criminal, you know.
I've heard some stories.
According to the rumors
making the round here,
she's no saint.
She poisoned 10 Yanome
a long time ago.
No, that just can't be.
I'm not so sure about that.
I'm also a Yanome prisoner.
She's important to you
but you don't know
anything about her, do you?
All right, since you must know,
I'll tell you the truth.
I deliberately steered
you onto the ship
headed here to Jananda.
Someone talked me into doing it.
I don't know much about them
but we got on the same boat.
-Huh?
-Hm?
Hey, wait!
Where are you going?
Come on, hang with us.
One thing's clear to me.
I don't want to
be with you guys.
You're all a bunch of liars,
you're not normal.
Wait a minute, pal.
What the hell do you
mean, I'm not normal?
Because you can keep smiling
in a place like this.
(Laughs)
(bats squeaking)
Are you there, black thing?
What is it?
This is a complete
waste of time.
Can't you put an end to all this
and take me to Pioran
with your powers?
I only assist you when
I'm sure the experience
is one that will help you
to grow and become stronger.
Stop it, I don't
care about that.
I want to see Pioran, all right?
Are you done with the
so-called tournament?
I don't want to do that anymore.
It hurts.
Beside, the next match is
going to be one-on-one.
I don't want this,
I don't want to kill anyone.
I don't want them to go
through that suffering.
But don't you remember?
You've already killed
several humans.
The most recent one, being
a young man named Gugu.
No, never!
I never tried to kill Gugu.
If it hadn't been for you
and the fact you were there,
he would not have died.
Wait, why would you
even say such a thing?
That's not the same
and you know it.
I'm not accusing
you of anything.
I just want you to understand,
death of the flesh
is a phenomenon
that everyone
ultimately confronts.
There are times when humans
have the ability to
choose when they die.
Gugu was given the choice
of continuing to live,
but he didn't make that choice,
instead, he chose to
shorten his own life
in order to save yours.
In a sense, he committed
a form of suicide.
The same dynamic
goes for the humans
who decide to
participate in the arena.
They take a chance
hastening their own deaths,
but do it to gain something.
You have no reason to suffer
over the fate of humans
who have chosen their
own time to live or die.
Fine, forget it!
I'll rescue Pioran myself.
(insect chirping)
(footsteps)
(groaning)
(fireworks exploding)
(grunts)
Damn it, if I were stronger.
Hey there, immortal.
The tournament is in two hours,
so heads up, you
better be there.
Don't you look at me like that.
By the way, I forgive you for
your verbal abuse yesterday.
Tonari, we need to talk.
One of our guests has
suddenly vanished,
I'm wondering if you
know anything about it.
The immortal one?
He's right over...
-Huh?
-No, not him.
I'm talking about a female,
the woman who came from Yanome.
(men roaring)
She seems pretty
determined to win.
Isn't she a guest?
She's a guest!
The captain is going
to be so furious.
This scent,
I recognize it from somewhere.
(ground cracking)
What was that sound?
Huh?
(digging)
(yelps)
(mole squeaking)
No, no, don't die.
You have no reason to suffer
over the fate of humans
who have chosen their
own time to live or die.
This animal didn't
make a choice,
it wasn't trying to die.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I swear, I didn't
do it in purpose.
Why was it trying
to dig a hole here?
The entire area's
covered in stone.
Now, I'm small enough
to get through the crack
where it was digging.
Where am I?
I can't see very clearly.
But I think I know
where I'm going.
All right, I'm almost--
[Mole Fushi] What are you doing?
Put me down! Let me go!
[Uroy] The tournament's
about to start.
[Mia] Is that immortality guy
actually going to
show up for this?
(sighs)
(startled)
He fell right out of the sky!
How cool is that?
He didn't fly here, did he?
You set? It's time
for round two.
Are you ready?
Now we begin the battles
between the eight champions
who survived the first round.
It's a series of
fights to the finish.
First up, from Block Two
and ready to rumble,
the veteran holy warrior,
Berserker of Zumla!
From Block One, entering the
arena apparently unarmed,
we have The Immortal Boy!
Can he pull it off again?!
(low growl)
Maybe I can scare
him into losing.
I'm not afraid of you.
(grunting)
Amazing!
(weapon clanking)
Please stop it and surrender.
You are never
going to defeat me.
[Spectator] Don't
you stand there.
[Spectator] Come on, fight back.
Stop it, please.
What could you possible
gain from this?
I'll tell you something, kid.
There comes a
point in one's life
when he needs to flip fate
right over on its head.
Now that I've eaten your
flesh, am I immortal?
It's no use, I can't
scare him at all.
(wolf growls)
well then, how about this?
That didn't work.
Alright then, how about this?
What's the matter?
Are you afraid or something?
Why wouldn't you attack me?
Come on, let's rumble!
What else can I turn into?
A crab?
Or that small
animal from earlier?
Oh, both of those are stupid.
(laughs)
I should've chosen
something more intimidating,
something terrifying and strong
that would have caused
him to run away.
Otherwise, what was the point?
What was I thinking just now?
What point am I looking for?
Is there no purpose to all this?
It's wrong of me
to demand purpose
in another person's life.
That sounds familiar,
I remember hearing
words to that effect.
From some one close to me.
I remember now.
It was this person.
(crowd amazed)
So beautiful.
I want a bite.
My body feels so light.
Come one, just a little taste.
(grunts)
Are you alive?
(groaning)
(crowd cheering)
[Announcer] Once again, we
have witnessed a miracle!
With a beautifully timed blow,
the Immortal Boy has defeated
the Berserker of Zumla,
and now moves on
to the third round.
(closing theme music)
Preview
[The Beholder] Tonari
offers to help Fushi
rescue Pioran from
her imprisonment.
But Fushi finds he is
unable to fully trust
this somewhat mysterious girl.
A Girl Named Tonari