(opening theme music)
(Parona whimpers)
What happened? Why am I...?
So Parona...
Tell me...
What purpose are
you supposed to find
if your life doesn't end and
you go on living forever?
[Fushi] Where would I even begin
looking for such a thing?
It's just too hard.
What did you ultimately
accomplish in your life?
Tell me, were you
happy when you died?
Oh, sorry, it's wrong
of me to demand purpose
in another person's life.
[Fushi] I feel like she
was talking about me.
[The Beholder] What
a fantastic vessel.
Parona of Ninannah.
I'm glad she died
sooner than I expected.
[Parona] Stop it.
Everything you're saying is
making me sick to my stomach.
I respect your feelings.
But after a while, you'll
find there's no reason
to be hurt every
time someone dies.
And when you do grieve,
you'll find pain
has the important function
of promoting growth.
[Parona] Get lost.
Wow. Scary things
happen around you.
You don't have to tell me. I
know what I did was horrible.
I feel bad for tricking you
and bringing you
onto this island.
And that goes for both of you.
But listen. I was desperate
to find a way out of here.
And promises were made
if I delivered you.
So, hey, anyway, the
reason I dropped by
was to ask you something.
Do you want to come eat with us?
[Parona] No.
(Tonari sniffs)
Wow, you smell so good.
And your hair, it
feels so smooth.
What do you use to wash it?
Oh.
(giggles) Your skin
is so soft and fair.
Not many people are
as lucky as you.
Where in the world did
this form come from?
More importantly,
how'd you get it?
Tell me something about
this girl you're channeling.
A Girl Named Tonari
(Parona grunts)
Welcome home, Tonari.
Dinner is waiting for you.
Here's something for you
to drink, immortal person.
What's in that thing?
It's cows blood.
We all pitched in and prepared
great feast for tonight.
I'll pass.
[Mia] What an ungrateful jerk!
[Uroy] After we went through
all the trouble of making this!
Sorry, everybody!
You had a rough
time in the arena.
You didn't want to
kill him, did you?
When are you gonna
stop following me?
It's fine. I get it!
You must have been going
through some things.
Oh no, what are you
doing? You've got to stop!
-Please! Life is precious!
-Huh?
I know you might
now believe this,
but there are some people
who deserve to die.
Like that guy you fought
today, for example.
He had already
murdered 50 people.
You should have shown no
mercy and just killed him.
You know something? I've
been thinking about it.
I wanna become like
the bow to your arrow.
I'd guarantee you one thing.
As the bow, I'd bring
out all of your strength.
I'm not going to let
anyone control me.
Am I clear? Now, go away.
(Tonari sobs)
Come on.
Tell me, how can I
make you like me?
You can't.
Pioran is still a captive
because of what you did.
I'm sorry. She's important
to you, isn't she?
[Parona] She's
like family to me.
Even if she's a murderer?
[Parona] So you say. I believe
in the Pioran that I know.
I get it.
You want to support her
because she's precious to you.
My dad was a killer, too.
So I was faced with
the same problem.
I believed in him. That he
never could have done that.
But, I'll never be
able to know for sure
because he's dead now.
Not knowing made
me feel helpless.
That's when you came along!
I thought you'd be able
to help me change my life.
That's why I brought you here.
Oh, great. Thanks a lot.
[Tonari] As soon as we
made it to the island,
your friend Pioran was gone,
probably locked up somewhere.
I don't have any proof, but
I'm sure that the person
who told me to put
you on the ship
is responsible for
whatever happened to her.
Huh? Is that person
on the island?
That's interesting. I
didn't even think about it.
I can ask everyone
here on the island
to help me find out who it is!
I swear, I promise! I'll
work with you to save Pioran!
That's nice, but...
Come on, don't be shy!
Sometimes, to change
the course of fate,
you'll find you need to
work with other people.
Oh, all right! What
was your name again?
Tonari?
Right on the money!
Okay! I'm going
off to investigate!
I'll see you later!
Almost forgot...
Remember to try and laugh
whenever you're feeling sad.
(Tonari giggles)
Hm.
[Fushi] Tonari, huh?
I still don't think
I can trust her.
She said some people
deserve to die.
How can she be so sure? And
under what circumstances?
If you can change something
for the better by dying,
then that's a meaningful death.
Parona never thought highly
of that kind of thinking.
She wouldn't think highly
of me, either, I imagine.
But I want to earn her respect,
even if she's not
here to offer it.
That's about all I
can do at this point.
I want to help someone, the
same way she and Gugu did.
Maybe this is my chance!
Mm, I made it!
I'm in the right place!
I can tell from the scent...
(Parona sighs)
Pioran's around here somewhere.
(Parona grunts)
(rocks crash)
(Parona pants)
Damn it!
Pioran!
[Pioran] Wait! I
know that voice!
(Parona sighs happily)
Pioran, it's me!
I've come to help you!
[Pioran] Fushi? Is that you?
Where is that voice coming from?
I'm in Parona's form!
So I think that means
she must have died.
[Pioran] I see.
Knowing her, I can only assume
she must have died
an honorable death,
probably protecting someone.
"An honorable death"?
[Pioran] Fushi, I'm in this
cell because I wasn't careful.
You need to leave this island
immediately without me.
You could do it easily, by
becoming a fish or a bird!
But why?! We're
leaving here together!
[Pioran] I'm a criminal, kid.
I get caught all the time.
I'm always in and
out of jail cells.
I'm just back where
I'm supposed to be.
I couldn't care less about that!
I'm coming up there to help you!
[Pioran] Don't be a fool!
This room is locked
from the outside.
You may be able to get in,
but then how am I
supposed to get out?!
That's a problem.
[Pioran] Listen,
Parona loved March.
If you want to make
her death meaningful,
do what March would
have wanted her to do.
Commit yourself to doing
good for those most in need.
Help the weak get through this
life so they don't suffer.
[Tonari] Hey, immortal!
I got some useful
information for us!
Come back up, all right?
[Pioran] Go on! Get
out of here, Fushi!
Mm.
I promise I'll save you!
I promise!
I wish I could say
"I'll save you,"
and be able to do it
without hesitation.
What does the word
"hesitation" mean?
We should turn in, so we'll
be ready for tomorrow.
Hold on. You said you
had something to tell me.
Useful, you said? So spill it.
Hm?
You gonna play dumb again?
I said I had useful information.
I never said when I
was gonna spill it.
I will tell you everything,
if you win the third round.
[Announcer] The third
round is about to begin!
There will be two
elimination battles.
Two of those contestants
will be moving on
to the final round!
Immortal...
Just go for his
head like last time.
You gotta rattle his brain.
Do that, and you won't
have to kill him.
(crowd cheers)
[Announcer] Begin the match!
(Parona grunts)
(Nando grunts)
(Parona gasps)
(Parona grunts)
[Fushi] He won't let
me get a kick in!
[Spectator] Get it over with!
(Parona grunts)
(Nando and Parona grunt)
[Parona] Oh, shit!
(Nando grunts)
(Nando groans)
(crowd cheers)
-Get him, immortal!
-Right.
Listen, now is your
chance to surrender.
(Nando groans)
[Fushi] He's not gonna
back down. What do I do?
Should I hit him one more time?
(crowd yells)
Hey, I'm coming for ya!
(Parona gasps)
(Nando gasps)
Are you crazy?!
Stop it! What do you
think you're doing?!
-You gonna refuse
-Don't make me sit
-To kill him again?!
-Through this shit!
[Spectator] This
is taking too long!
(weapons clang)
(grunts) I don't get it.
-(Nando groans)
-(Parona gasps)
(Nando groans)
The winner is the Immortal Boy!
He will be moving
on to the finals!
(crowd cheer)
[Fushi] His injury is my fault.
Congratulations!
Let's hold a proper
celebration with the gang.
[Nando's Brother] Brother!
(Fushi grunts)
Brother!
Immortal, I'm still alive
for now.
(Fushi sighs)
This is awful.
I'm so pissed off.
Why didn't you kill me?
Because I think
giving out pain is bad
so I don't wanna have to do it.
(chuckles) What the hell?
You're an odd one, for sure.
Why is a person like you
even participating
in this tournament?
Because I'm trying
to help someone.
That goes for me as well.
My mother was brought here
as a criminal and imprisoned.
She's dead now.
I would have escaped
right after that,
except for one
small complication.
Because your brother was here.
That's right.
I guess I'm pretty stupid
to want to protect
such a goofball.
(Nando's brother chuckles)
You're a brother
with a good heart.
I know someone who's
a lot like you.
I never thought I'd meet
such a person on this island.
A person who'd sacrifice
himself for someone else.
Pioran says that's honorable.
What would Parona
say about that?
If I win the tournament,
I'm gonna take you
two off this island.
[Both] Huh?
[Fushi] I didn't
mean to scare you.
I thought I'd see
what it was like
to be someone like
you for a moment.
Is that weird?
[Nando] Not at all.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Huh?
Excuse me, are you
done yapping yet?
Sorry, gentlemen,
but if you want
to keep talking to my client,
you're gonna have to pay
me a fee for the privilege.
Why do you keep following
me? It's irritating.
Listen to me, buster. I'm
doing you a favor here.
I'm trying to keep the
bad bugs off of you!
Bad bugs?!
Ugh. Where are they?
(Tonari giggles)
By the way, you said
you'd give me information
about Pioran after I won.
Well, I won so tell me!
Okay, fine!
The commander of our
boat, Captain Skyfish,
ate too many sweets
on his last trip over,
and by the end of the voyage,
he'd put on 15 pounds!
There you are. I told you.
Come on.
(both grunt)
Wait a minute!
That doesn't have anything
to do with Pioran!
How is that useful?
-(Tonari sighs)
-You're not fooling me anymore.
Stop it! You're always lying.
Why don't you try telling
the truth for once?
Hm.
Mr. Immortal, you could stay
here with us for the night,
if you want to.
That sounds great.
Listen here, boy!
Back off! He's coming with me!
[Nando's Brother] (sighs)
This happens all the time.
The fire won't start.
(fire crackles)
How's that?
Great! Thanks so much!
Fushi, return to your
boy form immediately.
[Gugu Fushi] Huh?
They're coming.
[Islander] Hey! You're the
immortal one, aren't you?
Yeah. Why?
Why are you turning everything
upside down around here?
Am I? If so, I
didn't realize it.
Gentlemen, do you have
some kind of business
with my client?
We islanders put our lives
on the line every day,
but not you!
Not only do you refuse
to fight, you won't kill!
You go out there and crush
your opponents' spirits!
You must be thinking
you're better than us!
Hey, I apologize if
I did anything wrong.
Sorry.
We all live by certain
rules on this island.
Oh, come on, now.
This island's rules aren't
even really enforceable.
It's a lawless mess here.
Listen, there's no victor
if there are no victims!
Not that I expect
an immortal like you
would ever understand the basic
concepts of life and death!
(islanders yell)
I happen to be the one
who brought him here!
Understand?!
Talk to me if you
have a complaint.
(Tonari grunts)
(Gugu Fushi gasps)
Hey, what you do that for?
(islander grunts)
Tonari!
How could you do that to her?
-(Nando grunts)
-Brother?
You stay behind me.
(Tonari groans)
Are you all right?
Hey, what's going on?
Where's that
rumbling coming from?
Huh?
(Gugu Fushi groans)
[Islander] What the...?
(Nando grunts)
(Nando's brother moans)
[Islander] What
the hell is that?!
Amazing!
[Fushi] Hurry!
Huh?
Just run!
Right now.
(Nokkers growls)
It's the same one as last time.
I'll blast fire on
it like I did then!
Wait, how did I use fire again?
Immortal, what is that thing?
Did you summon it to fight back?
None of you have left yet?!
Get out of here while you can!
It's just me that
it really wants.
All right. You didn't summon it.
So, are you able to beat it?
Yeah.
This time.
Now, don't follow me! (pants)
Whatever you say.
Over here, Nokkers!
Be careful of quick kills.
Those are the moments when
it will steal your vessels.
Good. There's no one here.
All I have within me are
Parona, the wolf, the crab,
and that small furry thing.
What can I do to
stop his attack?
(Fushi gasps)
There's an opening. That's it!
I can do it!
I'll bite it apart!
I can see this is
gonna take me a while.
(Mole Fushi squeaks)
(Fushi pants)
It's gonna kill me again.
Feel the power of
Janandan chair fighting!
Uh! Huh?
Tonari!
What are you doing out here?
I was clear. I told
you not to follow me!
When there's trouble, am I
someone who just runs away?
Forget it! I happen to
be Tonari of Jananda!
-(Fushi grunts)
-(Tonari gasps)
What the hell are
you talking about?
Get lost! The Nokkers
will kill you!
It's happened before!
Uh-huh.
Those things are called
"Nokkers", you say?
Stop playing around. Listen!
Someone has already died while
trying to save me from them.
Mm.
(ground rumbling)
(Tonari gasps)
(Fushi grunts)
Come on now. Aren't
you glad I'm here?
I would be way better off alone!
(Tonari gasps)
(Nokkers growls)
How dare you show
up out of the blue
and mess with our land?!
(Fushi gasps)
Yeah, take that, you freak!
[Mia] Tonari!
[Uroy] That thing is
completely made of hard rocks!
How do we fight it?
Rocks, huh?
Let's employ Chapter
Seven of the Escape Plan!
[Mia] We're doing
that now? Really?
Yeah, it'll work.
[Uroy] All right, then.
(Fushi gasps)
Everyone, run!
(islanders yell)
What am I supposed to do?
I can't save them all.
(islanders yell)
Think, Fushi!
There has to be something
you haven't tried yet!
(Nokkers growls)
(Fushi gasps)
Wow! It didn't work.
Let's target a different spot.
(ground rumbles)
[Tonari] Split up!
You gotta aim between the rocks!
Let me!
(Fushi grunts)
[Tonari] You suck, pal!
Oh.
Parona, give me your strength.
One more.
This bow is a lot lighter
and easier to use.
Maybe it'll be more accurate.
[Islander] Hold it steady!
(islanders grunt)
(Uroy chuckles)
He did it!
Come on, men, follow his lead!
Tonari, we're out of gunpowder.
Oh.
It's all right. We have
as much as we need.
(Oopa sighs happily)
(Nokkers growls)
[Mia] Look at that!
You can see the ocean.
(Oopa sighs happily)
[March] You know what?
I just want to learn everything
I don't know about the world.
Becoming a grown-up means you
get to know everything, right?
I've got you back!
I've got March.
[Fushi] And Oniguma, who
March cared so much about.
And most of all, Gugu.
(islanders chatter)
Now these people are
suffering because of me.
I'm sorry I brought you all
this trouble. (sniffles)
Hey, no one died. We did good!
Sometimes, to change fate,
you need to be able
to work with others.
If you fight with
lots of arrows,
it increases your
chances of success.
Hm?
What's with the droopy face?
You think I'm not making
sense again, don't you?
[Fushi] Thanks, Tonari.
Hm?
I just said,
thanks.
Uh...
Mm? What is it?
Nothing, really!
But I have to say, I never
thought I'd hear that from you!
(all laugh)
[Tonari] All right! We did it!
(closing theme music)
Preview
[The Beholder] Fushi and the
five children of the island
celebrate their victory
over the Nokkers
and discuss their dreams.
Feeling relieved
that they survived,
Tonari reminisces
about her past.
The Children's Dreams