[The Beholder] After his
confrontation with the nokkers,
Fushi lost some of his
memories of the past.
It was a costly price to pay.
He lost March's agility,
Oniguma's might,
and Gugu's ability
to breathe fire.
Since he was unable to make
use of any of these powers,
he struggled in desperation
as he tried to take down
the relentless nokkers.
But in his moment of peril,
the people of Jananda
Island banded together
and came to Fushi's aid.
In a concerted effort
the nokkers were defeated
and Fushi was able
to reclaim his past.
It appears that this island may
be the school at which Fushi
will find the guidance
he needs to continue
his growth as a person.
(opening theme music)
The Children's Dreams
All right, let's celebrate
our victory today.
We won!
[Everyone] Cheers!
[Oopa] You need to drink
this, Mr. Immortal.
It's cow's blood.
Second helping?
Yep.
So now that we're all together,
tell us the rest of your story.
What is it the man
in black told you?
Well when I transform,
it's always into a person or
animal who I've met before
who has since died.
He says the nokkers are
here to take those forms
away from me.
The reason the creature
you saw looked like a bear
was because it had
stolen that form from me.
Hold on, you're saying
you can turn into a bear?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, wow.
So wait a second.
Then why can't you
defeat the nokkers
by just turning
into one of them?
Now that is genius.
Know what, I haven't
tried that before.
But I've got to tell you,
the nokkers aren't quite
what you think they are.
To start with they're
not really things.
I gotta ask, does that man,
does that asshole in black
control you?
I'm just doing what he
says for one reason.
I don't want to start
forgetting people.
Hey, on a positive note,
what are your dreams
for the future?
Like what?
You know, things you
really want to do.
I guess the main thing is
to be able to defeat the
nokkers by myself.
That's a weird dream.
No, it's super cool.
I didn't mean that
kind of dream.
How about something
more ordinary?
My dream is simple.
I want to become a model
for a famous artist.
The problem is I
don't know enough yet
to have those kinds of dreams.
That could change,
especially if I leave here,
go out in the world, and
learn a lot more things.
That's true.
The dream of everyone
sitting in this room
is to leave the island.
Once we do, we're gonna
find a place that suits us
and live free.
I want a ranch where I can
raise a ton of animals.
And me, I wanna become a doctor.
In my case, my dreams
already been granted.
What was that dream again?
I've watched the sun every day
and always wanted to
know where it came from.
The sun comes from the ocean.
Oopa was born right
here on the island.
She doesn't know
the outside world.
What's your dream Tonari?
My dream?
I've been thinking about that,
my dream is I want
to surprise my dad.
But how, I thought you
told me your dad was dead.
You told me you're
gonna leave the island
and become a writer.
Yo Tonari, the final is set
to start tomorrow at noon.
And I asked Captain Skyfish
about procuring a ship.
I got bad news.
I just couldn't
convince him to do it.
I'm not surprised.
What, he won't let
you use the ship?
I'm sure there'd be
a way to work it out,
if you could help.
(everyone groaning)
Okay, let's eat.
We need to fill up that
belly to get you in
shape for the final.
[All] What, this
is all you've got.
Oh, just stop complaining.
Go ahead, eat all you want.
Oh boy.
Hold it, tell the truth.
This food came out of
your body, didn't it?
You should really try it Tonari,
it's the best ramen
I've ever had.
Nah.
(every loudly chewing)
Hey, everyone, what's
happened to you?
(calm music)
[Hayase] That western morning
glory is very effective.
I'm sorry, but I'd
forgotten about that.
(curious music)
It took me a while
to get up the nerve,
but I'm finally going to ask
him to eat with us today.
It's pretty simple.
I want to bring joy
to everyone around me
because they bring me joy.
(curious music)
(Tonari gasping)
(calm music)
Immortal.
Sorry for bringing your here.
Yeah.
(calm music)
To whoever reads this,
this is my story.
Hey Ligard, tell me
something, what's your dream?
My dream is to surprise dad
when he comes in and
discovers my book.
What's this?
Who left this book here?
It's very interesting
reading I must say,
but I wonder who
could have written it.
It has to have been my daughter.
See?
Dad's home Tonari.
[Tonari] I was seven
years old at the time.
Welcome back, we
missed you, honey.
You're just in time for dinner.
That sounds pretty good to me.
[Tonari] According
to one book I read,
a person's fate
remains in God's hands
until they turn seven years old.
I remember it was a chilly day.
(Tonari yawning)
(Tonari gasping)
When I woke up, I found my
mother dead on the floor.
For whatever reason,
the church decided that my
father had murdered her.
In my land, murderers were
sent to Jananda Island
for the rest of their lives.
I found myself faced
with a dilemma.
Should I stay in the village
and live as an orphan?
Or should I leave for the
island with my father?
I decided to follow my father.
I believed in him.
No one could convince me
that he had actually
murdered my mother.
On the island was
a world of people
who had given up on traditional
manners and behavior.
Because the population
was made up of criminals
and their families, the
society had developed
its own distinct culture.
People were granted
freedom of all kinds.
And when I say all kinds,
that included murder.
There was no one
to enforce the laws
because there were no laws.
Of course there were good
people too, but not many.
Most of the people we
spoke to were obsessed
with this tournament held
to determine the leader
of the island.
But it didn't take me
long to understand the
truth of what was going on.
These people weren't
looking for a leader.
They were just satisfying
their lust for blood.
[Elan] I've decided to
enter the tournament Tonari.
What, why would you
do such a thing?
I heard that some people
who won the tournament
became the island leader and
after a while left this place.
Yeah, but even if that were
true, it's too dangerous.
I'm aware of all the dangers,
but it's the only
way we'll get out.
All the islanders keep
an eye out for runaways.
I figure it's safer if
we leave officially.
Sweetheart, I'm sorry for
what you've gone through.
You must really hate it here.
It's just that these people
look like they're having
too much fun killing
other people.
From now on it'll be too
dangerous to be together.
Once the tournament's done,
we'll meet at the port of Ipo.
Don't you worry.
I'm not gonna die honey.
(crowd cheering)
[Tonari] I prayed that
when I opened my eyes,
my father would be
the last man standing.
(man grunting)
(Tonari whimpering)
(man laughing)
But I couldn't see him.
I couldn't find him anywhere.
What a waste.
Is that it for the first round?
Yeah, but there's going
to be more coming.
Dad, where are you dad.
Are you here?
Where are you?
(owl hooting)
I haven't been able to find him.
Maybe he's not here.
[Man] I think that our new
leader is going to be great.
He's the strongest
one I've ever seen.
His name is Elan. G Dalton.
(Tonari whimpering)
(somber music)
(Tonari grunting)
[Elan] Happy
birthday my darling.
Keep track of your dreams
and write them in this book.
Your loving father,
Elan G Dalton.
(Man groaning)
I'm so sorry Tonari.
He's dead.
I guess the poison worked.
That's what you get
for killing Cleff.
Serves you right.
[Man] What do you
think we should do with him?
[Man 2] Throw
him in the water.
Ready, one, two.
[Tonari] I had no choice
but to forget the past.
The day I turned eight, I
decided to begin my own story.
(Tonari crying)
[Mia] Why are you crying?
[Tonari] By the
time I turned nine,
I'd found myself a family.
There were a lot of children
in the same situation as me
and we banded together.
So tell me, what do you wanna do
when you leave this place?
By age 10, my friends and I
began discussing our dreams.
I'd started to smile
for the first time
since I'd come here.
When I turned 11, the five of
us began plotting our escape.
By the time I turned 12,
I volunteered to take on the
work of importing prisoners.
It was my one opportunity
to leave the island.
I had hoped it would
be our means of escape,
but the sailors were watchful.
Ow!
Get the hell outta here now.
All you people from the island
need to stay away from us.
At age 13, I realized
that outsiders
didn't want us around even if
we hadn't committed a crime.
They made me doubt
who I really was.
And then finally at
age 14, I met him.
He was so pale.
You need to get him
onto the ship somehow.
Trust me, he will win
every battle he enters.
And in the end he
will become a legend.
Before long he'll
upturn everything,
the whole island and
your fate as well.
Guide him and you'll
have a chance to be free.
[Tonari] She was a visitor.
I'd never seen her before,
but I'd heard that people would
sometimes come to the island
to watch the tournament and
buy people that they liked.
(adventurous music)
However, what she told
me turned out to be true.
As soon as he came
to the island,
everyone was captivated by him.
After all, he was immortal.
People who've been
around longer than me
say that in every story
there's a turning point,
but this might be that moment.
No, not might be.
It must be the moment.
(Fushi grunting)
Hey Pioran!
Fushi?
You're such a fool, but
I'm so happy you're here.
Pioran, I'll get you
out of here real soon.
I don't know what you're
planning on doing,
but this room's locked
from the outside.
If Oniguma helps
you, you'll be free.
Here's the deal, the final
round of the tournament
happens tomorrow.
Once I win, we can
both get on a ship.
We can leave with dignity.
Thank you, Fushi.
You always come through
for your friends.
The guard's keeping
watch for me.
I'd better go.
Listen, don't put
yourself in danger.
I'll be fine.
Bye now.
[Announcer] At last
the time has come
for the final round.
This battle will determine
the next leader of the island!
(somber music)
Immortal, just a minute.
If you have trouble
knocking your opponent out
with your hands
and feet, use this.
It's Oopa's blow gun.
Thanks Tonari.
Sure.
At first I actually thought
that you might not come.
Glad I was wrong.
Don't worry, when I win,
you'll all have your freedom.
[Announcer] Please
welcome our combatants!
(crowd cheering)
(dramatic music)
It's been a while, hasn't it
Fushi.
You remember poor
little March, don't you?
A girl who had built up a
world of hopes and dreams,
till they were cut short.
(Fushi gasping)
I know you.
You killed her.
You did that.
Ah, you're right, that was me.
But you have no need
to worry about her.
The truth of the matter is
that death brings freedom.
(dramatic music)
[Man] A bear!
Take her down Mr. Immortal
(Fushi growling)
(dramatic music)
Why what's wrong?
Is something the matter Fushi?
(dramatic music)
Bet you expected an easy win,
to tear my chest apart
like you did last time.
(Fushi growling)
(dramatic music)
That didn't satisfy me.
I don't think you're going
to be able to defeat me
while you're
occupying that body.
(dramatic music)
Why are you here Hayase?
Did you think you
could defeat me?
What did you expect
to accomplish?
I have a real bad
feeling about this.
Tell me something,
how does it feel
controlling Parona's form?
She's so soft, light,
and nimble isn't she?
I thought you might enjoy her.
Think of her as my
special gift to you.
(dramatic music)
(thunder booming)
I wasn't sure how
I should kill her.
I would have felt bad
slicing her stomach open,
so I decided to attack her face,
but that was just too much work
'cause she wasn't
dying fast enough.
So I slit her throat
and cut off her head.
It was a rather pathetic
performance for me.
I should have been able to
finish her in a single blow.
Because of my incompetence
she suffered much more
than she needed to.
So you're telling me
that you killed Parona?
Of course, didn't I
just tell you I did?
You're gonna pay for that.
(Hayase chuckling)
(dramatic music)
You're not able to defeat me
no matter what form you take.
You may be immortal,
but at this very moment
you're quite feeble.
The western morning
glory is quite potent.
(everyone gasping)
[Man] The immortal
freak is incapacitated.
[Announcer] We have a winner
in the final battle
of this tournament.
It's the birth of a
new island leader.
Immortal.
(crowd chattering)
(closing theme music)
Preview
[The Beholder] At the end of
the elimination tournament,
an unexpected
proposal from Hayase,
their newly crowned leader,
stirs up the people of Jananda.
Afterward, she captures
the incapacitated Fushi
and plans to make him her own.
The Defeated