All right, let's celebrate
our victory today, we won!
[Everyone] Cheers!
[The Beholder] The
battle with the nokkers
brought about a change
in Fushi's relationship
with Tonari and the
rest of the children.
Hey, on a positive note,
what are your dreams
for the future?
Like what?
You know, things
you really wanna do?
I guess the main thing is
to be able to defeat
the nokkers by myself.
[The Beholder] Before
going into battle,
Fushi promises Tonari
he'll win the tournament
so that they can all
leave the island.
It's been a while, hasn't it,
Fushi?
You remember poor
little March, don't you?
A girl who had built up a
world of hopes and dreams,
till they were cut short.
[The Beholder] Fushi's opponent
in the final confrontation
of the tournament was Hayase,
who had made her way to
Jananda Island from Yanome.
(dramatic music)
Why are you here Hayase?
Did you think you
could defeat me?
What did you expect
to accomplish?
(dramatic music)
Tell me something.
How does it feel
controlling Parona's form?
She's so soft, light
and nimble isn't she?
Think of her as my
special gift to you.
I thought you might enjoy her.
So you're telling me
that you killed Parona?
Of course, didn't I
just tell you I did.
You're gonna pay for that.
(dramatic music)
[The Beholder] There
are some who say
the essence of freedom is to
never be captured by anyone,
but the argument can be
made that there is merit
in being captured.
(dramatic music)
In fact, it can be a stepping
stone toward evolution.
(opening theme music)
Can't be, there's no
way he could lose.
Tell the truth Tonari, does
this mean we can't leave?
(everyone sighing)
[Fushi] This is the worst.
The Defeated
Ladies and gentlemen, I
declare the final battle
to be officially over.
Please acknowledge the
results and cheer the winner
of the tournament, and the
new leader of the island!
I want to thank everyone
for taking care of my Fushi.
My Fushi?
(dramatic music)
Don't look at me, I
hadn't heard about this.
I come from Yanome.
My name is Hayase.
I apologize for
taking the liberty
of joining this competition.
There is something that
I'd like all of you,
the people of Jananda, to hear.
I propose that we work
together in the coming days
and months to protect
this immortal boy,
this peculiar being
we have with us.
(Tonari gasping)
Five years ago I found
him in a feral state,
unable to function on even
the most basic of levels.
The boy couldn't even speak.
I took care of him
for over six months.
Perhaps because he wasn't
fully matured yet, he ran away.
As you would guess,
I was horrified.
I searched desperately,
but he evaded all my
efforts to locate him.
I followed rumors of this
monster across the lands.
And then finally I arrived
here and discovered him.
She's totally talking
out of her ass.
It's nothing short of a miracle
that I was able
to track him down.
Hey!
What you're saying
doesn't make any sense!
He's here because you
made us bring him here.
Isn't that right?
No, the truth is that's not
an accurate interpretation.
You brought him here by
the will of the heavens.
What?
The heavens have been
seeking strong warriors,
such as yourselves.
He can't fight this evil
alone, but he needs your help
if he hopes to be victorious.
That mountain of stone that
attacked your town yesterday,
I'm sure some of you must
know he was the first
to courageously stand
up to face it head-on
despite the danger to himself.
And that there were many
brave people who volunteered
to jump in and
fight alongside him.
I don't know what that
stone creature was
or whether it will
return to attack again,
but no matter what this boy
will need people to aid him.
Know this, what you
have here is a being
with many capabilities.
Only through him can you
ever change your fate.
He's the only one who can do it.
Is it true, was he
sent to save us?
I believe he was.
Our dreams of freedom are
finally going to be granted.
But despite all of
this, as his discoverer,
I have the responsibility
to oversee him.
People of Jananda who have
been chosen by the heavens,
please join me as
we create an army.
Together we will build
an unbeatable force.
-[Spectator] I'm in!
-[Man] Excellent!
[Spectator]
What are ya, crazy?
[Spectator] You want
us to worship that demon?
[Spectator] You're
not from Jananda are you?
[Spectator] And the
immortal's not from here either.
Let me be clear in my
position, the choice is yours.
The truth of the matter
is I'm not interested
in ruling over this island.
In fact I fully intend to
give away the rights I've won.
I've picked a Jananda citizen,
a talented leader named Tonari.
[Spectator] Tonari,
who in the world is that?
[Spectator] I've
heard that name before.
On Captain Skyfish's
ship, I think.
Let's scoot.
Yeah.
If by chance, you're not
satisfied with that choice,
then by all means
make a decision
based on the rules of this land.
I make a solemn promise
I won't interfere.
[Spectator] Kill Tonari!
[Spectator] Where is she?
[Spectator] This
tournament's not valid!
[Spectator] I agree,
start the next one already!
This is all kinds of bad.
I knew we should've kept a
closer eye on that woman.
Right, but what do we do now?
To those who follow me I
guarantee a life of abundance.
I promise every one of you
a life free from hunger.
You won't have to work again.
Just listen to what
I say and pass it on
to your friends and neighbors.
(dramatic music)
By this symbol I
shall serve this land,
the holy island of Jananda!
(crowd cheering)
(door creaking)
(Fushi sighing)
I'm pathetic.
Hey, what's wrong?
Whining already?
Six whole months.
That's all it's been
since you left us.
It feels a lot longer than that.
Don't forget Fushi, you're
going to live for an eternity
if you keep thinking that way.
How will you ever manage?
I'll just have to
get used to it,
including the fact
that Parona's dead.
I think about it sometimes
and wonder to myself,
how would I react if I were
told I was gonna end one day?
I might be immortal, but
what's my purpose here?
I haven't accomplished anything.
Come on, boy, what do you
think you have March for?
And Gugu as well, he's with you.
It's not exactly
like they're with me,
but a lot of times I
sure wish they were.
No they're there.
You can become
anything you want.
You can reinvent yourself.
That's what makes you
such a special being.
You know something,
you're right, all of you.
I have to keep going
for the other people.
Those who can't start over.
But before that, I'm going
to save Pioran and my friends
and get them off this island.
However, in order to do that-
Looks like it's
time to have fun.
What are you gonna
do with that woman?
You going to kill her?
(Fushi whimpering)
What are you doing?
Stop it, help, somebody!
What's happening, I can't move.
Oh, you poor thing.
You're completely helpless.
(Hayase heavily breathing)
We'll be together
very soon Fushi.
Immortal, where are you?
Hey immortal, you
need to wake up now!
Immortal, where are you?
We're here to help!
Right, my Fushi my ass.
That ugly pig.
(Fushi whimpering)
(Hayase heavily breathing)
Of all times, now?
It seems the drug hasn't
completely worn off yet.
(owl hooting)
Tonari!
That room, next level down!
Hurry, come on!
Halt!
All of you stop.
Ligard!
(guards grunting)
Immortal!
He's gone.
[Uroy] Did we get
the wrong room?
[Hayase] Is
something the matter?
Where's the immortal?
If you want to find him,
you'll have to go deep
underground to the sanctuary.
But that would be futile.
Once he's there, no
one can touch him.
(calm music)
[Tonari] Captain Skyfish.
Well, hello there Tonari.
What in the world brings
you to this place?
Why don't you tell us what
our island leader is thinking?
I'm thinking we're
getting out of this place.
We're leaving with the
immortal and his friend.
That's a pretty bold statement.
How will you find a ship
that'll let you on board?
Oh, you mean you don't know?
With the powers he possesses
the immortal can make a ship
bigger than the Skyfish
in just five seconds.
Huh?
Let's go.
That's our fortune
you're trying to steal.
I can't let this go unpunished.
This is pretty straight forward.
Either you stop this or
I'll be forced to kill you.
Sounds like she
means to do that.
You have no intention
of giving him up.
I'm right aren't I?
Tell me something, just when
did he become your immortal?
Oopa use your blow darts!
Oopa!
Put her down captain!
Why are you doing this?
Listen to me everyone,
if you don't submit to her,
she'll order her
men to kill you.
(owl hooting)
Come Ligard!
(everyone gasping)
You all have 10 seconds.
You can stop
resisting and go home,
or choose to die
where you stand.
-10, nine, eight,
-Tonari.
-I'm ready for you lady.
-Seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
(everyone gasping)
Immortal.
Commander Hayase.
Just stand back!
Move and I'll kill her.
I'm serious, I'll slice
her with this blade.
I thought I had locked
you up someplace secure.
How did you get back here?
What you carried off
was an empty husk.
-(dramatic music)
-(Fushi whimpering)
(dramatic music)
An impressive move.
Listen to me closely.
I understand that
you want to use me
to accomplish something.
Fine, I'll let you.
The trade off is you
let the others leave.
That's the price you must
pay for me to remain here.
Immortal.
The new leader will be leaving
the island very shortly
and will travel
to the main land.
She will sail there on the
Skyfish and during the trip
will be guarded at all times
by the soldiers of Yadome.
At the leader's discretion,
we will entertain requests
to book passage
for any residents
who would like to leave with us.
[Man] Take me!
[Woman] Please captain,
I have children.
[Spectator] Take me
too, get me out of here.
Silence everyone,
just listen to me.
We can only take up to
700 people on the boat.
The leader will determine
who those people will be.
Well time to choose.
Who will be coming
along with you?
I've decided to take with
me all my close friends
and an old lady named Pioran
and any child who is
aged seven and younger.
What do you mean you're
only taking kids?
What's so special
about seven and under?
We have just as much
right to go as they do.
This is bullshit!
(crowd booing)
The children here are
innocent, understand?
And because of that
they deserve the chance
to choose their own fate.
The only way they'll
ever be able to do that
is to leave this island.
Are we clear now?
That's the last word about this.
If you're interested,
come forth and form
a single file line.
Go, take care of each other.
[Child] We will mother.
Here you are sweetheart.
Please watch over her.
Please, sir, let
me get on the ship.
I turned seven last week.
If you're seven I must be five.
You two are staying
here with me.
I'm not going to leave.
I'm sorry, you have to.
I not going brother.
I wanna stay here with you.
Nando, get on board
with your brother.
But didn't you say-
It's fine, I'm just carrying out
the immortals promise to you.
(calm music)
See you later immortal.
I can't believe it.
Are we really
leaving this place?
You are.
Fushi, I'll be waiting for
you at the port in Zedan.
I suspect this woman
will be dead of old age
before the two of you
are ever reunited.
(Pioran grunting)
What do you think you're doing?
(kids grunting)
Take them away.
[Guards] Yes Ma'am.
Don't worry your
pretty little head.
We'll take them all
with us, I promise.
Don't you dare hurt
any of those kids!
I'll make you pay if you do!
Now then, it's time for
us to be going as well.
(wind howling)
[Man] Tonari.
Boss!
Untie me.
Right.
[Tonari] Was
everyone knocked out?
No, just you kids.
For crying out loud, it
hasn't been five minutes.
Those bastards said you'd be
asleep for at least two hours.
It doesn't make any sense.
Why are you the only
one who's awake?
Good question.
Hey, guess we're leaving.
There's not much we
can do about it now.
Boss.
I'm gonna need you to help me.
[Man] Are you sure
about this Tonari?
Are you really gonna go
back there to save him?
Shh, don't worry about it.
Just lower me down.
What am I supposed to tell
the others when they wake up?
Tell them I'm out for awhile.
That when I came
to my stomach ached
and all the bathrooms were full.
Hey, what are you doing?
Shit, there's no good answer.
(guard grunting)
Ligard!
I can't believe it.
Thank goodness you're okay.
I was so upset.
I thought that woman killed you.
Steer to the right.
There's a blind spot there.
Be careful, don't get caught.
Okay, I'll try not to, thanks!
Where are you going?
Are you abandoning us?
Take care of the kids for me.
I'll see you soon!
You really mean that?
Keep everyone safe till
I get back, promise me?
Yeah, I promise.
What the hell's
going on out there?
We have to alert Commander
Hayase right away.
I'm the one who decides
if someone gets turned in
on this ship.
(calm music)
[Tonari] Now that I've had
a moment to think about it,
I've decided to add another
chapter to my story.
Of course I'm talking about
the story of what adventures
lay ahead for an
unknowable life form.
I have to say I was
relieved to find out
during the tournament
You're gonna pay for that.
[Tonari] That there are things
that can drive
him over the edge,
so in spite of his background,
it makes him seem kind of human.
And in the end, kind of like me.
No matter what, I want
him to be in my future.
(closing theme music)
Preview
[The Beholder] Tonari
returns to Jananda Island
in an effort to help free
Fushi from his captivity.
While there they find themselves
battling the nokkers once again.
While helping Jananda
fend off an attack
To Continue On