[The Beholder] Fushi
and Tonari were about to
escape Jananda, but more
Nokkers suddenly arrived
on the island and
launched another assault.
The Nokkers took over
the bodies of the dead
and they attacked in hordes.
Fushi fought alongside
Tonari and her friends
as they tried to
protect the Islanders,
but Oopa, Mia, and
Uroy were each defeated
one after the other.
(dramatic music)
Fushi came to the realization
that those who were willing
to fight for him are the
same ones he must protect.
(opening theme music)
(wet cut)
It's all right, you
can come out now.
I've cleared this entire area.
Thank you so much,
Commander Hayase.
We owe you.
Take these people
to the shelter.
Make sure they
arrive there safely.
Yes ma'am.
(slow dramatic music)
This is certainly not a
pleasant sight to look upon.
So what do we do with them?
(slow dramatic music)
Well well.
Hi there, monster.
What are you trying
to accomplish?
I wonder, could it be that
your trying to possess Fushi
the same way I am?
If that's the case, you ought
to do it more intelligently.
How do you expect to
take control of that boy
when you present such
a repulsive appearance?
You'll never be able to
overcome Fushi with brute force.
Do you follow me?
You have to find a way to
treat him with kindness
the same way I do.
(dramatic music)
Wandering Rage
Hurry Tonari,
we're almost there,
just a little bit further.
We've found the Nokkers nest.
I see.
Apparently I need to
be a little more savvy.
What's better the face
or the gut perhaps?
The neck would be quicker
and the most humane.
-(dramatic music)
-(Hayase groaning)
(bear growling)
Fushi,
are you planning
to wipe me out?
Really now?
(Fushi growling)
(chuckle)
How terribly amusing.
What seems to be the problem?
You've never had a better
opportunity to kill me.
Why are you waiting?
Could it be that you're actually
afraid of killing people?
You better hurry and
get it over with,
because if you don't your
two friends are going to die.
(Fushi roaring)
Are you all right?
Yeah I'm fine.
(dramatic music)
Don't get up yet!
My arrows.
(dramatic music)
Are you hurt?
Immortal.
You saved us.
Stay behind me.
I'm gonna burn 'em out.
(dramatic music)
(gasp)
[Tonari] You've destroyed
them all, haven't you?
[Sandel] You did it!
Well done Fushi.
Because of your efforts, there
are only three Nokkers left
on the island.
Three?
So tell me immortal,
where are Mia and Uroy?
(somber music)
(Tonari gasping)
Mia, Uroy.
Immortal?
(Fushi crying)
I'm sorry.
I couldn't save them.
(Tonari crying)
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
No, it's all my fault.
I'm the one who
brought all of this on.
It's been like this my whole
life, ever since I was eight
I've been making all
the wrong choices.
I don't know why I expected
anything different.
I'm so selfish.
I was never in my right mind.
[Sandel] That's not true Tonari.
No one could have predicted
something like
this would happen.
It isn't your fault at all.
It's just not!
(Sandel and Tonari crying)
Fushi, once the Nokkers
get close enough,
they're going to plant their
roots back into the earth.
Guys, those aren't
your friends anymore.
You need to stay away from them.
What are you gonna do?
What should I do?
It's awful.
Tonari, you decide
for the both of us.
[Tonari] I'm sorry, I can't.
Should I do it?
I understand your feelings.
Should I kill them for you?
Tonari!
These children are
only sleeping, for now.
If you give me permission,
I can take the responsibility
off your hands.
Please, I want to
do this for you.
Let me kill them, all right.
This is an entirely
selfless act I'm offering
with no strings attached.
I want you to be
a beautiful being,
a being who has killed
no one, hurt no one,
and taken from no one.
Even if it's a friend whose
body has become possessed.
Come on, isn't that
what you want Fushi?
Isn't that the real reason
you couldn't kill me earlier?
The bottom line is this,
you don't have the
courage to sully yourself.
And guess what, I'm willing to
support you in that decision.
In the final moment when
push comes to shove,
I'm ready to step in and
take on that dirty role
to protect you.
Listen to me, just
let go of Tonari.
I'll hear you out after that.
Don't move please.
Unless of course you want
to see her burn to ashes.
Why are you bringing
Tonari into this?
I'm negotiating with you,
it's as simple as that.
Let me ask, why
would you reject me
if you'd then be forced
to kill your friends
and become sinful and
dirty in the process?
The truth of the matter is in
this situation, you need me.
I have a simple
proposal and it's this.
Rather than killing her,
I'll save you the trouble
and kill those other
three children instead.
If you're in favor of
what I've suggested here,
all you have to do is
nod in my direction.
Go ahead, do it
to save this girl.
(slow dramatic music)
If I can choose
my fate right now,
then the path I choose is this.
Oopa, Mia, Uroy, I'm coming.
I'm on my way to you now.
(dramatic music)
(Tonari gasping)
Thank goodness I
got to you in time.
Don't worry, I just put
her to sleep for awhile.
Come on, stand up.
(Tonari whimpering)
(somber music)
(islanders chatting)
[Tonari] Oopa's parents,
they sold her for a
single silver coin,
but she still grew up to be
caring and compassionate.
She was such a good girl.
Mia was my first real
friend on the island.
She was the reason
I was able to smile.
Uroy was like a
wonderful older brother.
Anytime something happened,
he'd be the first one to draw
his sword to protect us all.
The truth is they were
all I had to live for.
I judged you before, sorry.
It was wrong.
I shouldn't have said
you weren't normal.
I didn't really know you yet.
It's fine, we knew
what we were doing.
We were resisting,
determined to overcome
being trapped here.
But you know, we found
ways to laugh about it.
That's right we did, and
you most of all Tonari.
Let's go men, here are some
more bodies to pick up.
Oh, island leader.
Why are you here?
I thought you left days ago.
Weren't these
children your friends?
Hadn't they left
the island with you?
We came back.
And then we all fought together.
How could this have happened?
These children were innocent,
they did nothing wrong.
And they died
protecting scum like us.
(men crying)
(somber music)
Immortal, the people
of this island
are all demanding a leader.
Because of that, I must ask,
are you willing
to speak to them?
No, I'm sorry I
just can't do that.
Everything that's
happened is my fault.
How about you leader?
Would you come address them?
Well you can tell everyone this,
a mountain of
corpses does nothing
but draw evil to the island.
We must stop all this
killing and help each other,
so that we don't die as well.
Thank you so much
for that leader.
I'll share your
message right away.
I hope the word spreads quickly.
Mm hmm.
[Sandel] So Fushi,
what happens now?
What's your plan?
Well I know this much,
more Nokkers will
come if I stay here.
I'll wander around the island
to make sure everything's okay.
If the people have what they
need, then I'll leave here.
[Sandel] That sounds good.
[Fushi] So what about you two?
We had a discussion
about that earlier.
We're going to
stay on the island.
(somber music)
Are you sure you
don't want to leave?
You can change your mind.
No.
There's lots of things
that need to be done,
like cleaning up
the tainted water.
I know that more criminals
are going to arrive.
They'll try to disrupt the
good things we've established.
I'm staying because I don't
intend to let that happen.
This Island's going to be a
place where the worst people
can be purified.
I'm going to build a
signpost so that most people
can experience a different fate.
I don't know if I can accomplish
all that I'm hoping to
being a 14 year old girl
and all, but I'm gonna try.
I brought the supplies.
Here you go.
Thank you so much.
Let me know if you
need anything else.
I'm ready and raring to go.
I may be skinny, but I'm strong.
How are you feeling?
You're looking much better.
Thank you my friend,
you've been amazing.
Not really.
[Sandel] There's still
plenty more food, eat up.
[Man] I'm eternally grateful.
[Tonari] Here let me
help you with that.
[Man] Come back
again when you came,
(somber music)
Thank you, Immortal.
(children chatting)
[Man] Hey you kids,
don't crowd him.
Give him some space.
(children chatting)
Well, I guess it's time
for me to be going.
Hey, take care of yourself.
You sure you'll be okay
taking that lady with you?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
What about you?
I'm more worried that
Hayase's men might try
to harm you guys while they're
out there trying to find her.
[Guard] Shout out
if you're here.
They might try.
But don't worry Fushi,
we're never going to
let those goofballs
get the better of us.
You have to get going.
Someone might see you.
Okay, thank you
both for everything.
Why?
You helped us more than
we were able to help you.
(Sandel chuckling)
Hey!
Immortal, take care of yourself!
Fushi, listen,
keep an eye out!
I just might come
visit you someday!
I'm kidding!
You know, you should
go with him Ligard.
You'll have much more freedom
if you're living out there
in the world, and some
day in the future,
maybe you'll be able to
guide me back to his side.
(calm music)
(Hayase sighing)
Tell me something.
What's been your
objective in all this?
Actually, it's been
pretty simple Fushi.
From the first time I saw you,
I just wanted to be with you.
And you were willing to
kill people for that?
I mean March and Perona!
Both those girls became
obstacles in my quest.
The two of them tried
to take you from me
and keep you for themselves.
I'm surprised you don't
understand what's going on here,
how I'm feeling.
The fact is I'm
in love with you.
I have been ever since
the day I first met you.
What?
I feel sorry for you, you don't
know what love is, do you?
Why don't you let me help?
I only need a little time,
which you could grant
by giving yourself
to me for one night.
It's all I would need
to teach you about love.
(Fushi growling)
Are you angry enough
to kill me, Fushi?
Please, the truth is I
want to be killed by you.
We both know the secret of
my death is that you and I
will then become one.
So do it.
Please Fushi, kill me, so
you can then become me.
I promise you I'm much
stronger than anyone else
you might have inside you.
Well, don't you
find that enticing?
Please don't go, Fushi.
You don't realize it
yet, but you need me.
I didn't watch where
I was drifting,
so I'm not sure where we are.
I guess if you wanna live,
figure it out for yourself,
just don't come near me anymore.
Fushi!
I hate everything about you.
When you die, I
won't feel anything.
I know that.
(somber music)
(Hayase screaming)
(dramatic music)
[The Beholder] Well Fushi
did you enjoy Jananda?
Can't say, but for now tell
me how to get to shore.
(adventurous music)
Ligard has offered to guide you.
In the beginning I hated every
day I was on that island.
I couldn't wait to leave.
But now,
I miss it a little.
(adventurous music)
Preview
[The Beholder] Pioran, she
has been waiting a long time
for Fushi, and though
he has been apprehensive
about the prospect
many times in the past,
he decides to spend his life
Echoes