Things have changed.
I'm not the same as I used to be.
I'm a different girl, and I have been ever
since the day I met that guy who insists he's a god.
Ugh.
I can still touch things even
without my body. That's cool.
Hiyori.
Hiyori!
Are you with us, Hiyori?
Yes?
Whoops. Was I asleep again?
Yes, you were. If you're not feeling
well, you should go to the nurse's office.
I'll be fine, I swear. I'm really sorry.
I'm so sleepy all the time. I hate it.
I've been feeling like this ever
since the incident with the bus.
And it's more than just drowsy spells.
The forecast says it's gonna snow today.
Cold snow.
Aw, man. That's no fun.
Snow. Cold snow.
Well, come on. Let's go!
You're gonna be late.
Oh right!
Nobody else can see what I see.
It's a being that dwells beyond normal people's sight.
A phantom.
White snow.
What's so special about me that I can see them now?
Hello! Wake up, sleeping beauty!
Wow, again? This is crazy!
Totally. I bet this insta-snooze trick
of hers comes in handy sometimes, though.
So she's a closet martial arts nerd and a narcoleptic.
That's a combination you don't see every day, huh?
No kidding. We should warn her
her panties show when this happens.
Yeah, that way she can wear something appropriate.
Something non-descript would work best.
Nah, something that's super cute.
This is all so strange.
Even so...
It does have its moments!
Whee!
I'm a bird! I'm a bird! I'm a pretty, flying bird!
Look at me! I'm a bird!
Phantoms can be found everywhere.
Lurking in the shadows of an alley.
Soaring through the sky.
Sitting on people's shoulders.
They're not the same. They come
in different shapes and sizes.
But they are all denizens of
the far shore. Devoid of life.
They're mostly invisible. The only ones
who can see them are young children, animals.
And, of course, those of us who roam
the divide between the near and far shores.
A black haze in the distance. So that's a "storm."
An area thick with despair that attracts
all kinds of phantoms. It gives me the creeps.
Yato told me a little about phantoms.
They possess people and then those people
lose all hope and spiral out of control.
That's what I'm dealing with,
and Yato still hasn't contacted me?
Ah, hello, there. Nice to talk to you again.
What can I do for ya?
Don't give me that! You said you'd help
with the phantoms and the tail and everything.
Yeah, yeah. I know, I know. I'll get to it eventually.
Could you be more specific? Exactly how
long is "eventually"? It's been two weeks!
Look, some unexpected stuff came up recently.
Stuff I have to deal with before I
can even think about doing anything else.
So I can't get to you quite yet.
Be straight with me. Are you really a god or not?
You doubt me?
Don't. I'm the real deal.
Do you know any humans who can do that trick?
You should be in awe of my magnificence!
You're wearing a tracksuit and
a weird bib around your neck.
That isn't really an awe-inspiring outfit.
You shouldn't judge people by the clothing they
wear. Didn't your parents ever teach you that lesson?
And it's not a bib, it's a fluffy-fluff scarf.
Fluffy fluff scarf?
Did you see that girl over
there? She's talking to herself.
Don't stare. She probably isn't right in the head.
Explain something to me. What's the
difference between you and phantoms?
Huh?
I mean, you have things in common.
You're invisible to most people.
And the same thing goes for phantoms, doesn't it?
Unlike them, I'm actually from the far shore.
I wasn't born from a human being.
I'm a god of war, born from a wish.
Yeah?
Yeah, between the two of us,
I'd say you're more like a phantom.
Huh?
Not again! I didn't even notice it happening!
Hey! You're a ghost! Ha, ha, ha, ha!
This isn't a joke, you jerk!
In all seriousness. This bare
form of yours isn't safe at all.
You should be careful.
A living phantom makes a very tempting target.
They will come for you.
They'll come, eager to corrupt your soul and consume it.
And once you're possessed by
a phantom you lose who you are.
You'll cross lines that shouldn't be
crossed, and you won't even hesitate.
Because what you'll find beyond may be a
living hell, but it's a pleasurable one.
Well, when you put it that way, would you fix me already?
I remember our contract, don't worry. You
paid your 5 yen piece. And it's non-refundable!
Yeah it's my money now. I'm saving
up for a shrine that's nice and big!
By the station with a wife and a separate
bathroom. Yes, a shrine just for me!
How is this, Lord Yato? Am I
massaging your right leg to your liking?
What about your left leg, Lord Yato?
Ah most agreeable.
I am Yato! An almighty god of war!
Now, then go forth and pick out the
peanuts from a bag of mixed nuts for me!
Yes! As you wish, sir!
Oh, yeah, I like that!
So, anyway, when will you get to my job?
Huh? Soon enough.
I told you to sit tight, didn't I?
You've been telling me that since
last week. I'm sick of waiting!
Oh, last week, huh? Well here's a proposition,
then. Call me "Lord Yato." It'll show some respect.
Do that for an entire week and
I'll consider starting your job.
I mean, seriously, who calls a
god by his first name, anyway?
I could call you something else.
Fine the truth is I'm not at 100 % right now. I
can't take on a big job. Not until I find a Regalia.
Okay, and what exactly is a Regalia?
Regalias are tools. They serve as weapons for gods.
When I have a Regalia I can cut down anything.
Oh.
So that why you completely unused right now.
So you use to have a Regalia then.
Did you lose it?
Why?
Lose a Regalia? No, she qui...
I fired her.
Regalias are people?
Well, they're spirits.
Oh. Really?
Hello! Thank you for calling delivery
god Yato. I'm fast and affordable!
Need help, you say? I'll be right there!
Wait!
I do not like that guy.
I got everything I need. Why
should I bother getting some dumb job?
I don't need work. My parents support me.
Do you see them, Hiyori? Those
are "lazy bums". Scary, aren't they?
I mean, it's not like I can't get a
job, it's just that I don't want to.
That's it! He's one of those lazy
bums mother was always warning me about.
But what now? It's not like I
have anybody else to turn to.
What should I do?
Your fists will guide you! Pave your own way!
That's it! I'll listen to the great Tono!
He's right! I can't rely on others for everything!
I gotta take matters into my own hands!
I've got it! If he needs a Regalia, I'll find him one!
Excuse me! What would you think about
being a Regalia for a guy named Yato?
Excuse me! Hello there!
A storm.
There are a ton of spirits in there.
I bet at least one will hear me out!
Wow. Never seen that trick before. You using toilet paper?
Yep. If you stick it on the wall like this, you can
get all the mold off without having it drip everywhere.
To be really thorough, I'd leave it
for half a day before rinsing it off.
Man, you really are a pro, aren't ya?
A pro?
I appreciate ya comin' over so quickly,
too. Maybe I'll become a repeat customer.
Please! That would be great!
Well, I'll leave ya to it.
Oh, by the way. Do you have an old toothbrush I could use?
Say what?
It's what you need for mold that's
particularly thick, like it is here.
You did a great job, kid! I just called you in for a
leaky faucet. But, this place has never been cleaner!
Thanks.
I feel bad payin' just 5 yen. I know! Here's a tip.
Ah, man, some god of war I am. How pathetic.
I spent my day repairing a leaky pipe
and cleaning up mold for chump change.
Now that's tasty! At least I got a drink out of it, huh?
Well, I'm already here. I might
as well crash at ol' tenjin's place.
Looks like business is boomin' for him!
How's it go again? "You can check out any time
you want, but you can never leave." Or something.
Looks like it's especially stormy out tonight, huh?
So that Hiyori girl's job request.
What am I gonna do abou...
Who's calling now?
Oh, great. Her again. This is really getting old.
Yeah, hello. What can I do for ya, Hiyori?
Hey! Sorry to bother you this late, but, uh...
I've got something. I-I think I
found a Regalia for you, actually.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Well... here he is! What do you think of him?
Lia-Regalia.
Run away!
You thought that could be a Regalia?
Sure, why wouldn't I? You did
tell me that Regalias were spirits!
That's an ordinary ol' phantom! A twisted ball
of emotions and curses! Can't you tell that much?
Well, yes! Actually, that's what I
thought when I first spotted it, too.
Smells nice!
But then I remembered what you said earlier about
not making judgments based on how things first appear.
This is how you chose to apply that
lesson? You've got awesome timing!
And there's one more thing, too.
I got separated from my body again!
Your timing seriously sucks.
Hiyori!
Oh yeah, that's right! I forgot. I'm
actually a halfway decent fighter in this form!
It's okay! I'm fine! I can take care of this guy myself.
Hey, there, ugly. Come and get me!
Here I go!
Jungle Savate!
Come on!
Hey, what happened? Your hand really
isn't looking so good. Are you o...
I'm fine. Don't touch me. Or it will blight you, too.
What do you mean?
A blight is a kind of defilement. One that can spread.
Unless you exorcise, or cleanse, it,
it'll stay there and eat away at you.
Smells nice.
Also, we need to talk about your backside.
What?
That thing ain't a tail. It connects your
physical and ethereal forms. Like a lifeline.
Nice smell!
If something happens to sever it.
Then you'll die!
No way! You mean I'm not wireless? That's not cool!
That's your worry? Listen, human! You're out
of your league trying to fight that phantom.
Don't do anything like that again!
But you said yourself that you can't
do anything without a Regalia, right?
Back off! I've been trying to find one, okay? I have to...
A young boy.
Not so young... looks to be in his teens, I'd say.
A difficult enough age for anybody.
Smells nice!
Uh, Yato.
I think he'll do.
Smells nice!
Spirit, you are lost and adrift. You
have nowhere to go and nowhere to return to.
Thus, I grant you a place to belong. My name is Yato.
Bearing two names, you shall remain here.
With these names, I make thee my servant.
With these names I use my life to make
thee a Regalia, fit to be wielded by a god.
Thou art Yuki! As Regalia, Sekki! Come Sekki!
A sword?
Yato!
No!
This is the land of the rising sun.
Your desecration shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god Yato. I now lay thee waste with
the Sekki and expel thy vast defilement! I cleanse thee!
Rend!
That's so...
Wait, was he just crying?
I found my body and brought it back!
It's so cold! What are you doing?
I have to cleanse the blight from my hand.
So all it takes is a little water?
This day wasn't a total waste, after all.
It's a lucky thing we ran into an
uncorrupted spirit. Really lucky.
The blade's the perfect length.
Wow! So that's a Regalia!
Cool!
It's looks sharp and shiny. Which I'm guessing is good.
Sure is. Name's Yuki. Or, less formally, Yukine.
Whoa!
It became a boy!
Yukine.
I am Yato.
I'm your master now.
I summoned you here from the far shore to be my Regalia.
You will remain by my side. You
need not return from whence you came.
Take this.
Go on. You've nothing to fear.
I don't want a stinky tracksuit.
Um, well, take this.
It's cold out here.
Can we get inside, already?
Hey. You hear me?
Are you cold? You can put on my fluffy-fluff scarf.
Thanks for the offer, really. But I think I'm okay.
Next time, on Noragami: "Bidden calamity."
Oh, go on, just take the scarf.
I'm gonna pass.