See! Here we have a little phantom.
What are you doing, Yato?
Good! We want that reaction.
Hate and fear will help you draw a borderline.
And what's that?
A borderline is what serves as a
regalia's shield. It's also his only weapon.
Now, then. You did some pretty nice work the other day.
I think you're ready for this.
Humph! Flattery won't get you anywhere.
It's real simple. Make your fingers into a halberd.
Then use them to draw a line like this between you and it.
Uh, okay.
Here goes!
Amazing! So that's what you were talking about?
Yep. Useful stuff. Phantoms can't cross it. It
acts as a boundary between "self" and "other."
Is it something you can do, too? Or-or even me?
No. You and I can't do this.
Borderlines are a regalia power.
Any regalia should be able to make one.
But creating one that's this strong without practice...
I've never known a regalia
who could do that. It's a first.
Speaking of the Regalias that he knows...
So, um. That girl we ran into down by
the water. Nora? She's a regalia, too?
Oh, Nora, huh?
How to put it...
I guess you could call her a friend with benefits.
Eh...
I've decided that I'm going to look after Yukine.
Huh?
You are? That's crazy. He can't
stay with you. It would never work.
It makes more sense for him to stay with me than with you.
You don't have a place to live or what
even resembles any sort of stable life.
It's all ex-girlfriends,
affairs, and friends with benefits.
You're depraved, irresponsible,
and unfit to be anyone's guardian!
Yukine is obviously better off in
my care. You'll just corrupt him!
Get away from her!
Stop that! What are you doing to the poor thing?
Ahh! Come on! I'm getting stung like crazy here!
Quit it! Can't you see you're hurting him?
You're gonna pull his arm out of the socket!
You think he's hurting, look at
me! I'm getting seriously stung!
Jeez! Are you crazy? What's your problem?
I told you! When he has naughty
thoughts, I'm the one who pays for it.
Every one of 'em stings me!
What do you mean naughty thoughts?
Ugh, please! You were just
talking about him living with you.
At his age, that's basically guaranteeing
a whole crap ton of dirty thoughts!
The answer is no! He'll be staying with me!
You know, I think it's really someone
else who has his mind in the gutter.
Unlike you, he's a good boy. There's nothing
to worry about. Now, come with me, Yukine.
No, Yukine! Don't you dare!
Your house is freakin' huge!
You must be really rich or something, huh?
Don't be silly. I'm just an ordinary teenager.
Yeah, well, this doesn't look very ordinary
to me. Are your parents around here somewhere?
We got lucky. It looks like
they're actually out late tonight.
Huh? You mean it's just you and
me? We have the whole place to our...
oh, no! Sh!
Ah, I thought I heard you, Hiyori.
Yeah, it's me, Sasaki.
Nice evening, isn't it?
I have a bath drawn for you. Feel free
to hop in whenever you're ready, dear!
Whoa! This is awesome!
Go ahead and make yourself at home you can stay in here.
Huh? Really? Isn't this your room, though?
No. It's my big brother's.
Your brother?
Yeah. He's a lot older than me.
He doesn't live here anymore, so the room's all yours.
Oh, okay.
It's great. If you're sure.
I'm not far. My room's next door.
Let me know if you need anything. Well, see you in a bit!
Looks like Hiyori's really living a dream life, isn't she?
Everything went as planned. We made a stealthy
entrance, unnoticed by our housekeeper or my parents.
Oh! Hi, you guys!
Surprise! We're early!
Lookie! We brought home a tasty snack!
Well. I think I'll have a
nightcap if it's okay with you, dear.
Oh! You're absolutely incorrigible!
This is the best part of my
day! And now for a little snack.
Don't eat too much, now. Have you washed your hands, dear?
What are you doing? You know you're
supposed to be watching your cholesterol!
But I was just having a little.
Your mom sure doesn't miss much, does she?
What are you doing here? This is my house!
Jeez what's the big deal? It's not
like they're gonna notice that I'm here.
The whole point was to separate
Yukine from your bad influence!
Speaking of, how's he taking it so far?
How do you think? He's thrilled, of course!
Do you think he really enjoys sleeping in a
different, random shrine every night with you?
Unlike this house, shrine grounds
and buildings are sacred territory.
Which means they keep US safe from phantom attacks.
Even so.
Haven't you ever heard that things go bump in
the night? That's the phantoms' favorite time.
Poor kid. I doubt he'll be able to handle it.
Huh?
The thing about him...
You see.
Is he's afraid of the dark.
Aw, man, I don't even know how long
it's been since I've had a hot bath.
What now?
I wonder what Yato'll do if I
decide not to go back to him.
Maybe he'll switch. Start using that girl instead.
But if he does, what happens to me?
Huh? Why do I feel like I know that smell?
Ah! Hold on, is it, is it because...
D-d-d-d-d-d-d...
Did Hiyori just take a bath in this water, too?
Ah! Here you are. I've been looking for you.
Hey, Hiyori! I found what I needed! Don't worry about it!
Gotta train harder. Build stronger
quads. Gotta master the jungle.
You need something, Yukine?
I woke you up. I'm sorry.
It's okay. Is something wrong?
Well, um. It's going to sound stupid, but
your dad turned off the lights in my room.
And I, well, y'know. I don't like the dark much.
Oh... I get it.
Well, want to sleep with me?
Huh?
It's okay, see? Come on in.
Oh no I can't really--
hurry up already, it's getting cold.
B-b-b-b-but I!
Yeah, it's been a while since I slept with someone, too.
You don't smell like a boy. You smell nice.
I like this. Lying next to someone.
It's soothing.
It's kinda nice not to be alone at night, you know?
Young man, just what do you think you're doing?
You jerk! What are you doing here?
Don't give me that, you little
punk! What were you about to do?
No, I...
listen, Hiyori said I could be there!
You're not ready to have girls in your
life yet. So behave. For now, I'm all you need.
When you say stuff like that, it makes me wanna puke.
And anyway, you've got a girl. A
regalia like me, but she's a chick.
So what do you even need me for?
Gonna be another stormy night.
Closing in on downtown. Location reached.
Incoming: Six o'clock!
We're done here.
I'm glad you came. This is fun.
Didn't have anything else to do, so.
Those look nice. You want a pair?
Uhh...
It is getting colder outside.
Let's see how much I have.
No! It's okay. I don't need anything, I promise.
Oh, come on. I want to get them for you.
But I'm fine, really! I mean, it's not like anyone can see
me, right? So, if I want something, I can just borrow it.
Hey! You should know better than that!
What you're doing's no different than stealing!
What? I said I'm just borrowing it.
I'll give it right back.
Well, it's still wrong. Here, give it to me.
The next time you want something
like this, just tell me okay?
Where did he go?
Hey.
Yato? What are you doing here?
Getting a little r and r. I'm not feeling so good today.
You are looking after him like you said, aren't you?
'Cause it seems like he's been gettin' in trouble.
How could you possibly know that?
Like I said before.
Master and regalia share mind and body.
I feel it when Yukine gives in
to the temptation to behave badly.
That's just how things work
for US. We're closely connected.
In that case, is the opposite true? Did Yukine get stung
when you swiped some of my dad's drinks from the fridge?
No, it's not like that. The pain
only goes in one direction, you see.
From regalia to master, which actually
makes sense, if you think about it.
After all, Regalias used to be people.
And people sin. Some more than others.
Resentment, fear, envy, desperation, sadness, greed.
Those emotions tempt Regalias to
do what they otherwise might not.
Acting on them brings pain. We gods feel that pain,
and from it we learn something of what it is to be human.
Listen, Hiyori. I think there are
some things I ought to clear up for you.
People decide what's right and wrong, but those
concepts don't apply to gods. To put it in simple terms,
gods get to do whatever they want. Even if
that includes hurting someone, or taking a life.
Someday, Yukine may need punishment. Divine punishment.
Yato.
But yatty did kill a regalia once.
He kills people, too, sometimes.
I-I have to go. I need to find Yukine!
Again? Of all the things to leave behind.
I screwed up. I wonder if she's still mad at me.
Crap! It's that late?
Damn it!
Hurry!
Faster! I hate the dark!
I'm scared.
It's dark.
I don't like the dark. Mommy. Please come and get me!
You stopped walking. You can see me?
Oh no.
You can see me! Everybody else out here just ignores me!
Well, these eyeball things try to
talk to me, but they're weird and scary.
This girl...
I'm waiting for my mommy, just like I'm supposed to.
She comes to pick me up after my tutoring session is over.
Oh, she does, huh?
She shouldn't be much longer.
Will you please wait here with me?
Just 'til six o'clock.
Sure.
Where is he?
I'm really sorry. I guess my mommy's running late.
Your family's probably worried about you, too, huh?
Family? I don't really have one of those.
Hey, I know! When my mommy gets here,
you can come home with US too, okay?
Don't worry. I'm sure she'll get here soon. Really.
No, she won't.
Hey! Come back here!
There you are! I've been looking everywhere for you!
Wait, don't go that way!
Huh?
You must be so scared.
Poor little girl... All lost and alone... in the dark.
But don't worry. It'll be okay. Your mommy is over here.
My mommy?
Come this way. Come to US.
Yukine! Use that thing Yato taught you!
First I have to make my hand into a halberd.
Damn!
Border!
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said your mom's not coming.
It's okay now. They'll stay
back. They can't cross that line.
Smells nice. Smells nice.
Smells nice.
I just noticed. You actually smell really nice.
Smells nice. Come here.
You smell really nice. Want to smell more.
Yukine!
More smell, please. More. Can I have?
More smell, please...
Boy smells nice. Mommy? Where?
Yato!
Yukine, you all right?
That big phantom... A girl, went into it.
Boy smells nice!
Help her! You have to help her, Yato! Please help her!
Very well.
Come Sekki!
This is the land of the rising sun. Your desecration
shall not be allowed. Hear me. I am the god Yato.
I now lay thee waste with the Sekki and
expel thy vast defilement. I cleanse thee.
No! Yato!
Stop!
Rend!
What the hell are you doing?
You were supposed to save her!
It's too late for that. Can't you
see? She's been completely possessed!
What are you saying?
Killing her is the only choice we have now.
Yukine.
Once it has been corrupted and
consumed by a phantom, a soul is utterly lost.
Its existence
can be nothing but a living hell!
You must do this. Show her mercy and free her!
Yukine!
Rend!
We've received word from
Kuraha, who's patrolling the city.
It seems that he saw Yato, slaying a phantom.
He appears to have obtained a new regalia.
I see.
How was your bath, Yukine? Nice and relaxing?
Yeah. Oh, and I used some shampoo. I think it was
Rose-scented or something.
I'm guessing it was yours, right?
Actually, it's my dad's hair-growth cream.
Your dad's?
Next time on noragami: "Scary person."