Hey, Yukine?
You awake?
I baked some cookies for you.
I'll just leave them by the door with some cocoa.
Hey, Yukine?
Dammit.
Border!
Why am I freaking out so much?
It's Yato's fault. Forcing me to kill that girl.
Stop!
Rend!
What you're doing's no different than stealing!
Damn! They won't get off of my ass! Even HiYori!
What the hell?
Hm? Hmph.
Damn kid.
Not in there, either.
Yukine's been so down since that last encounter.
And Yato hasn't even spoken to him.
I guess it's only natural for him
to feel this way after what happened.
Oh, hey! HiYori!
Hey!
Ami! Yama!
Don't you think that you should be at
home studying instead of wandering around?
What about you? We all have to take the exam.
Yeah, but we don't sleep through class all the time.
So we're pretty sure we'll be moving
on to the next grade with everybody else.
But we're starting to worry about you.
I'm doing plenty of studying, thank you very much.
Oh, hey. Have either of you seen a boy
wearing a green parka around anywhere?
He comes up to about here.
A boy, huh?
Yeah! He's kinda young.
Hm.
Oh, hello, Mrs. Iki? Your
daughter is in a torrid relationship!
And we're smack dab in the middle of exam season!
Ahh! No, don't listen to them, mom!
It's not like that, I promise you!
And you got a thing for ugly guys! I bet he's
hideous! Just look at your beloved Tono after he lost!
Don't show me that! I haven't gotten to that fight yet!
You better introduce us to your boyfriend!
Here's hopin' he looks like just like Tono!
Seriously, it's not like that!
Oh, man! I don't even know if the gods can help her now.
I actually would like to introduce
them to Yato and Yukine sometime.
Of course, there's not much point. They'd
probably forget they met them as soon as it happened.
And then...
I can't really pretend like I
know Yato all that well myself.
Man, that was too easy! Heh, hah!
Ha, ha! I can pretty much do anything I want!
What the hell's your problem?!
Yato!
Wanna tell me where you got this?
Um, well, HiYori bought it for me.
Uh-huh.
Yukine!
You've been with Yato? Oh, man, that's a relief.
HiYori, that was real nice of you to buy this for him.
Huh?
Uh. Oh, sure. I'm nice like that.
Man, I really can't stand kids.
That's one deep crimson sky.
Twilight serves as the boundary between day and night.
The people of this world, they
fear the darkness, and hide from it.
While the inhabitants of the other
world blend into the darkness and run wild.
With its reddish hue, the setting sun
blurs the distinction between the worlds.
As the evening shadows grow deeper
and harden into pervasive darkness.
This is the time when those lost in the
divide can most easily cross the boundary.
People once referred to this as the time of
day when the monsters emerged from their slumber.
Yukine, this time is known as...
The fiendish hour.
Oww.
Shh.
The hell?
Ya see what happens when I explain things to you?
I'm blaming you for the trouble that just landed on us.
I've found you at last god of calamity.
Hi, Bishamon.
Bishamon?
That's right.
The strongest war god that I wish I never met.
She's a god? Well, aren't you on the same side, then?
Why is she attacking us?
We tangled once a long time ago. And
she's been trying to kill me ever since.
Huh?
Then count me out of this one!
You can fight her on your own.
I dunno. I doubt she's gonna just let you walk away.
This is a matter of revenge for
her. She wants me and my Regalia.
Well thanks a lot!
My grudge may drive me to slay you both.
But the punishment of evil will make it just.
Come, Sekki!
Huh?
Wait!
You won't escape me!
Wait. The Bishamon, the god that punishes evildoers?
Revenge against Yato? She even wants to kill his Regalia?
If anything happens to me. I want
you to go straight to those two.
Do you understand?
Kazuma, I need you to track him.
Understood.
Target currently moving north-northeast. 2.1... 1.9...
The area is lightly crowded, but I
suggest restraint in your attacks.
Only one Regalia, abilities unknown.
Well, killing is the only thing Yato's
skilled at. Kuraha, deploy your pincer attack.
As you wish, milady.
You will die at my feet today.
Why the hell did you stop? She's gonna catch us!
Get off my ass. You're part of the
reason I'm so exhausted right now.
Huh?
Quit bein' such a pansy.
What? I am not a pansy.
I can feel it!
You've been stinging me nonstop with your crap!
How many times I gotta tell you that
your volatile emotional state affects me too!
Get it together!
But that woman. She's a god just like you.
Are you seriously gonna fight another god?
She's the one attacking us, okay?
And you're... gonna use me?
Obviously!
It's your job to kill what I want dead!
Everything Bishamon has with her, all of
her weapons, even her clothes and that beast.
They're all Regalias.
You're saying that lion's a Regalia?
You got it. On top of that, she's got Kazuma, who
handles her navigation and coordinates the other Regalias.
His all-seeing guidance makes Bishamon
the mightiest war god of them all.
Hey! Why aren't you hiding? She'll see us!
She'll find us no matter what!
I'm making a stand right here.
While I've still got some strength.
What? But I don't wanna fight her!
It's her!
So heavy! A full hit will snap the Sekki in two!
Catch him, kinuha!
It grabbed you! It's a Regalia?
I told you that! Now shut up and focus, Yukine!
Gaiki!
Locking on.
Targeting cervical vertebrae and
left humerus. Zero point in: 2... 1...
Fire!
Impressive.
Sorry.
Kinuha!
You evil scum!
How dare you!
I swear I'll never let you kill another Regalia!
Hold on. You've killed a Regalia?
Didn't I tell you to shut up, Yukine?
Get over it! You've been stalking me for years
now! Haven't ya got anything better to be doing?
Ya crazy half-naked tramp!
Your existence is an obscenity
to nature! I will eradicate you!
Suki!
The blade's dulled!
C'mon! Pull yourself together!
Damn!
Tch.
Kofuku!
Oh, hey, HiYori. What's going on?
Hi, Yori! Talk about perfect timing!
Which kind of Daifuku bun do you like better?
We have the kind with...
It's Yato! Bishamon's attacking him and Yukine!
Bishamon, huh?
Oh, jeez. I can't believe Bisha's still
trying to kill poor Yatty after all this time.
She called him... what was
it? A "god of calamity" I think?
What does that mean?
Just another way of saying
a god that causes disaster.
Huh?
Yatty's a scary war god. You haven't
already forgotten I told you that have you?
It was a long time ago, but Yatty did kill a Regalia once.
Wait a minute.
The Regalia Yato killed... does this
mean that it was Bishamon's Regalia?
This is only between Yato and Bishamon. It's
none of our business and I'm stayin' out of it.
Uh. But, Yato told me to come to you for help.
You just have to help him!
Please! What will he do without you?
You really are desperate to help him, huh? I
know, you've got a thing for Yatty, don't you?
Huh?! No, I don't! Honestly!
So he's blackmailing you then, isn't he?
Extortion? That's just awful!
There's not a single person who trusts him.
None of that. I still need his help with my body problem.
Don't you worry, Yori! I'm more than happy to help you!
Wow! Thanks!
You can just pay me your money offering later!
Huh?
Just remember you asked for this,
and don't blame me for the fallout.
So, where is Yato?
I'm actually not sure.
Oh, wait! Maybe I can find him!
Whoa! She has a cord!
She's a half phantom?
I've noticed that all of the
gods have a pleasant smell to them.
But that smell is slightly different for each one of them.
He's that way!
Yato.
Huh?
That lady,
the one that's chasing us.
Did you really kill her Regalia?
Yeah.
Then it's only natural she wants revenge on you.
Why'd you do it?
Because I wanted to, alright?
Nothing more.
So it's that easy for you then, huh?
Is what that easy?
And me?
Are you gonna kill me if I screw up?
Or if you just don't need me anymore?
Not that I matter to him.
Even without me.
He's still got that other Regalia, Nora.
You're stinging me again, dammit.
Seriously. Man up and get your head straight!
What?
Your fear is killing me here! It's
put me in a real slump! Freakin' wimp!
Hey, you're just as scared as I am!
What?!
Your hands are five times sweatier than usual, old drippy!
Who the hell you callin' old drippy?
I'm talkin' to you, aren't I, you moron!
Well it takes a moron to recognize
a moron! You freakin' moron!
Se-seki!
You're like a walking armory.
And c'mon.
Did you hav'ta take out all those trees? Did
the forest kill one of your Regalia's as well?
I can overlook some immoral
collateral damage to purge evil.
Well it's a good thing you've got the
power of righteousness on your side then.
Make you feel all warm and fuzzy inside?
Those will be your final words.
Whoa! We can't fight that!
That monster will tear me in half!
Yatty!
Found you!
Kofuku?
Lady kofuku?
Come to me, kokki!
Now pay attention to me, you two!
Is she?
Are you insane?
No more fighting!
What's happening? She blasted open a
vent! She can barely control that thing!
She's always causing storms with her kokki.
Phantoms are pouring from the underworld!
Lady Bishamon! We should retreat!
Stay the course! Kuraha!
Yato!
Kuraha.
Restraint.
Kinki!
Kazuma! Help kuraha.
Bastard!
Lady Bishamon.
We need to retreat for now.
He's right there! Just forget
about the vent! I demand justice!
Veena!
If you personally wish to be eaten
by phantoms, then go right ahead.
But tell me. Do you wish the
same for kuraha and the others?
Whoa, what in the world is that?
Dammit, HiYori, why'd you bring them here?
But wait, you told me to go to
them if you were ever in trouble!
Oh. But I didn't mean this time!
I just never really expected I'd run into Bishamon.
Oh, no!
Well, regardless, you should hide.
Huh?
And don't say my name.
Bishamon can't find out you have any connection to me.
Oh, right!
Out of respect for lady kofuku,
I'll let you live for today.
But I will kill you the next
time we meet with my own hands.
So try not to get any more blight.
Let's go, Kazuma.
HiYori! It's dangerous here, we've gotta go!
Right!
Nice work back there, kofuku.
Pretty impressive, huh?
I'm being sarcastic! You screwed everything up!
You ingrate! She saved your sorry ass from death!
Ow, jeez!
That hurt, Daikoku!
It was supposed to!
There were some really high-force
winds blowing through the city at sundown.
I heard a whole patch of trees in the
woods were knocked down. How frightening.
No good. It just won't cleanse.
Yukine, is this just not gonna work?
Yato. Try not to look so down.
Don't forget that you can always use me.
Nora.
That's a deep crimson sky.
HiYori. The word crimson...
"crimson" originally denoted the color
of a dye made from Kermes Vermilio, right?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Next time on Noragami: "Uncertainty and destiny."
You sure do know a lot.
Well, this is exam season.