If that doesn't happen very soon.
Then Yato will die.
So Yato was right.
You did steal it.
Why is he even using such a Regalia?
Sekki! I will re-forge you!
It'll be okay, though...
Won't it?
Ow.
Well, how 'bout that? Hello, there!
Wait! I'm not spying on you, I swear!
Seriously. He's telling the truth.
Now, would you like to explain why you're here?
It's for work. I was trying to tell you.
By the way, what part of the job
includes graffiti-ing the girls' bathroom?
You see, young one. I long for the
worship of all people, regardless of age.
Thus, I must be prepared to enter even a high
school bathroom if that's where the request leads.
I'm not buying it! What kind of client
would ask you to come here, you perv?
Allow me to introduce...
...our client!
I didn't mean to...
Don't hurt me!
Sorry. Very sorry. But I'm not being dirty or anything,
though, honest. I just had to get away from those jerks.
It's true.
My name's Manabu Ogiwara. I'm in Class 2-A.
There are these guys in my class.
They mess with me whenever we have a break.
So I hid. I figured this was
one place they'd never find me.
I'm sorry! It was a stupid plan!
I had no idea. Now I'm sorry. I
should've let you explain all this, first.
Yeah, I had a feeling it was gonna be something like this.
That's usually the case when I get called out to a school.
You've seen this sort of thing before?
Bullying is real common.
And I happen to be just the type of
guy victims call when they want some help.
I can see why. They're desperate
enough to clutch at straws.
Or at gods.
What did I ever do to them?
I hate this stupid school so much.
I wish I could go anywhere else!
You're getting angry because you can see yourself in him.
I get it, really. It's not fair. But
being pissed at him won't help anything.
Don't give me that! What the hell do you know about me?
I'm nothing like that whiny loser! And I'm sick and
tired of tagging along on these useless jobs of yours!
Wait! Don't go!
Not exactly a sweet-tempered kinda kid, huh?
You could learn from him.
In your case, it might actually be
helpful to let it all out like that.
Huh?
Here. You can use this.
I-I don't.
Remember this.
If you decide to fight.
I can't believe you gave him that! I
hope you have some kind of plan in mind!
Just adding some fuel to the fire.
I want Manabu to try defending himself for once.
How he chooses to do that is up to him.
I guess so, but couldn't you and Yukine handle it somehow?
By severing his ties to the bullies, maybe?
What's the matter?
You know...
...you did just give me a beating.
I think I'll... go lie down.
Was this a bad idea?
Being here could push Yukine too far.
Maybe to his breaking point.
Huh?
Hold on a second! What do you mean "breaking point"?
So he thinks I'm like that other
kid? What a joke. I'm not even alive.
As long as I've got this, I can't go anywhere.
I'm stuck with the least popular god ever!
This really sucks!
"Day Duty" "The class field trip"
"This month's goals"
"Guidance counseling"
Everyone wears the same thing.
Is this how I used to dress?
All rise.
Attention.
Bow.
Be seated.
I solved it!
So what do we have next?
Uh... Language Arts.
Lemme see your homework!
Man, do you ever do yours?
My folks are really pissing me off.
They seriously want me to quit judo.
The big tournament's coming up, though.
Oh, man.
So many kids, and they're all my age.
I can't believe you brought that with you again.
You know they're gonna take it up.
Don't be a narc.
That's it! Get 'im good!
Get him!
Awesome!
When did you level up, dude?
Sweet, huh? I had my brother help me.
Hey!
Can we all come to your house today?
Well... I dunno. I'm busy.
C'mon! We're your friends!
Friends, huh?
That must be nice.
They're so lucky.
It's those jerks again.
Why do they hate me so much?
Why am I so alone?
Why, dammit?
Let their bodies hit the floor.
If you don't like them you should kill
them, or else you could just die instead.
Say goodbye to the cruel, cruel world!
What makes a garden grow, grow, grow?
Great. These are bruised, too.
I keep telling her to be careful, but does she listen?
Hm?
Yeah?
Bishamon?
I mean, Lady?
Bisha!
Yay! Bisha's here! Bisha's here!
So, why are you here? And so heavily armed, too?
Sorry, I'm being rude.
Kura.
Aki.
Kinu.
Tsugu.
Kazu.
I'm Kuraha.
My name's Akiha.
Hi, I'm Kinuha.
I'm Tsuguha.
And I'm Kazuma.
There you go. You've met all my weapons.
Good afternoon.
We've come today in hopes of getting an augury.
We dealt with the Phantoms that escaped
the Vent, but we'd like to take precautions.
Will you help?
In this area here, and... let me think.
I don't get it. What're they doing? What's an augury?
Oh, that's right. I keep forgetting you're
still new here so there are things you don't know.
Every once in a while, our lady comes here to
consult Lady Kofuku about where more Vents will open.
Eenie, meenie, miney, moe...
Vents almost always open at
locations she divines like this.
Of course, one could always argue that
they open because she points them out.
Now, now, that's not kind to say.
Vents are tricky.
They open when you least expect
'em, but doing this can help a bit.
It's not surefire, but it's the
best thing we've got right now.
Another one?
There are a lot.
Your work's not over yet, Bisha.
It looks like you've still got
a lot of Phantom hunting to do!
So it seems.
Lady Kofuku, I didn't realize
that you and Yato were acquaintances.
Do you see him often?
Once in a while, sure.
These Vents... You wouldn't be
opening them intentionally, would you?
As a means of keeping me busy,
and thus away from Yato, perhaps?
Now you're just being silly, Bisha!
No...
Despite what you might think about
my lady, not even she would do that.
I assume you're aware of my history with Yato.
Yep!
Of course, it's not really any of my business.
Still, if something were to happen to Yatty.
Well, then, there'd be a Storm.
I should be going.
My Lady Kofuku! What?
Threatening the Bishamon like that! And I
thought I couldn't fall for you any harder!
That was fun.
I have a feeling the worst of it's not over yet, though.
You think those two are going to keep fighting, then?
That's not what I'm worried about now.
Yatty was blighted, remember?
I wonder how he's doing.
No answer.
He should still be at the school
It's strange, though.
I can't smell him.
I wonder what's going on.
He seemed really worn down, too.
Hello? Is there anybody in here?
A-ha! I found you!
If left untreated, the pain will intensify.
The blight will spread throughout the body.
Hello.
I know what you're thinking! Don't get any dirty ideas!
It was innocent. I was just
checking something, that's all!
You know you're crazy, right?
So, Yukine still hasn't shown back up?
To be near me? No.
He's at an age that can be difficult and
dangerous for anyone. And Yukine is stuck there.
Who knows what he's up to?
A Storm's brewing.
So which tortured youth does it belong to?
Manabu, I think.
I know, right? It was my idea.
That's awesome!
Did you see the look on his face?
Or maybe not.
Later, man.
Oh, it is you. I thought I got a whiff of garbage.
What's your problem?
You got something to say to me?
Really, dude. You're actin' kinda freaky.
You should kill him.
Kill him now.
Come on.
We were havin' some fun, is
all. I mean, can't you take a joke?
Having some fun?
That was fun?
Remember this. If you decide to fight...
It's only fair to arm your opponent, too.
You're messin' with me, right?
Cut him now.
Cut him deep.
Cut him deep now, and you'll be free for good.
Cross over the line, now.
Over the line.
Cross over the line. It'll feel so good.
Hurry.
Cross it.
Cross.
Cross over the...
The line.
Cross over.
Cross the line.
It will feel so good.
It will set you free from them all!
All it'll cost is your humanity.
Manabu!
Are you okay?
Wow.
That's some impressive self-restraint.
I like to be prepared.
If things'd gone south, I had purification water ready.
I remembered what you said.
That's how I held back.
I couldn't use that thing to hurt someone.
I really wouldn't belong anywhere if I did that,
'cause I wouldn't be human anymore.
It's up to me.
Whatever they do, I have to stay strong.
You did a good job.
Well, I guess they'll go back to just ignoring me.
Man, I tell ya. Kids these days.
They think life's a competition to
see who can make the most friends.
Really, one is enough.
Find that one unique person and you're all set.
Do you think he'll be all right?
I mean, can you be sure those jerks
won't try to get back at him for today?
Didn't you see? The other kid peed
his pants. He won't be telling anyone.
I hope things work out and he
finds a good friend, like you said.
I think he's gonna find what he needs soon,
which is something I'd like to do.
Huh?
Find somebody who's completely...
...unique.
Why.
Why?
Why is this all that I get?
Come back!
Why are you leaving me behind?
Can't you just take me with you?
Please!
So, then.
Figured it out at last.
You can't go back over to that side.
This is your existence.
You'll never belong where you used to anymore.
Why are you ignoring me?
Hey!
Now you can finally see what it is you really want,
but you also know that it can never be yours again.
But don't do it, Yukine.
No matter how you feel.
Damn it.
You can't, okay?
You can't cross that line!
Damn it.
Poor, lonely little boy.
A crash? What was that?
Yato!
Everyone! Get down!
Hurry!
What's wrong with you?
Oh no!
The blight. It's spreading everywhere!
Yato!
Say something! Please!
What now? What should I do?
If anything happens to me...
I want you to go straight to those two.
This is how the blight feels?
And he's been enduring it for all this time?
Feel better?
Hey what happened to him?
You happened to him, Yukine.
Huh?
Every time you do something bad, you hurt him.
He suffers the consequences for you.
He's in so much pain.
And has been, but he's endured it.
No!
But I...
I should've listened to him
and tried to get you to stop acting out.
It's my fault. I'm sorry.
What are you waiting for?
Don't snack too much! I'll have
dinner on the table soon enough.
'Kay!
Huh?
Hm?
We sure are popular today, huh?
Huh?
Help us!
Please! Yato needs you!
Ya...
Border!
A Borderline?
Take it down!
Please let us in!
Daikoku!
Kofuku!
Don't just stand there!
Can't you see?
Yato is going to die!
When the east wind blows...
My lord, perhaps you could recite
a new poem every now and then.
Oh, Tsuyu.
The young are so impulsive!
Next time, on Noragami: "Name."
Well, my lord? The poem?
Yes, yes. Just a moment.
You can't rush divine inspiration.