Yukine. Tend to the shop once you're done in there.
'Kay!
Nice.
The oden's ready now.
Great. Glad to see you're off to such a good start.
Hey! Good morning, you two.
Hey! Good to see you!
So you really did pick up a part-time job here, huh?
Well, it's just.
I need to. I wanna pay back the money I took, y'know?
Aw, Yukine.
I may be made out of stone, but even
I coundn't say no when he told me that.
You were on the wrong path, but it looks
like you've finally straightened yourself out.
Uh. Yeah, that is part of it. But it's also
because Yato doesn't ever make any damn money!
Oh, yeah. Don't you have a
favor you were gonna ask Hiyori?
I said that wasn't a big deal!
What is it?
Um, well, uh.
You're getting set to move onto a new grade, right?
He was hoping you wouldn't mind passing your old
textbooks on to him if you still have them around.
He wants to start acting like a normal kid again.
It's cool if you don't want to...
Of course I don't mind! You can have them all!
Huh?
What is wrong with you guys lately?
Oh, there you are! I've been looking for you two.
Just so you don't forget. You owe me money, too.
Oh, c'mon, Yori. Don't tell me you already
forgot that you asked us to save Yatty for you.
Cuz we did the work. And this is how much we charge.
Five yen? I can do that.
5 million, and we did help you twice.
Ten million?
Oh, don't you worry. A girl as
cute and smart and capable as you are.
I'm sure you can earn that amount it in no time at all.
Wait, Kofuku. Hiyori's still in
school. What about the student discount?
Oh, good point. So. We'll call it one million.
Good deal! 90 percent off! That is one serious bargain!
And this is why it pays to do
business with the god of poverty.
You still haven't even fixed my body
yet! And now you've put me in debt?
You will help me pay this off!
Man, what fighting federation does she belong to?
Tenjin!
I wanted to drop by and say thanks for your help!
I heard you really let yourself
get put through the ringer.
Yeah, I guess so.
What, you guess so? How could you ever
let your blight get that out of control?
Your Regalia had you on the verge of death.
Well, the Sekki has incredible potential. I
couldn't just throw away his talent like that.
And besides that, I wanted to reforge him properly.
I intentionally let my condition get that
bad. just to give him a stern wake-up call.
Well. I suppose I understand your method.
Yeah, but regardless. You guys really saved my butt,
especially you, Tomone. I guess we're still friends.
That's Mayu for you. She is a gutsy, dependable girl.
All thanks to a certain lowlife who took her in.
Well, I am one hell of a teacher.
Oh, yes, and your method follows the four Cs, I believe.
Are they friends now?
I can't tell.
Come, come. Why don't we talk somewhere else?
Hey. Aren't you missing one of the
Regalias? I think her name was Miyu?
Unfortunately. She was kicked
out for stinging Lord Michizane.
She was corrupted?
You see. What happened to you,
Yukine, is actually very contagious.
Just seeing or hearing about it can affect others.
A single sting to a master results in banishment.
Lord Michazane has never once
made an exception to this rule.
To harm others or yourself, whether intentionally
or not, is to betray the master who named you.
Banishment is actually seen as an
act of generosity after an ablution.
Because a new master might take you
in. If you're lucky that is. Otherwise.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
It simply couldn't be helped. But please. You mustn't
let this bother you, no matter how upsetting it may be.
It might have an effect on Yato.
Believe me when I tell you this,
Yukine. We understand how you felt.
Regalias are easily corrupted if
they don't maintain their borderlines.
Ultimately, we're still Far Shore
beings who dwell alongside Phantoms.
You must be careful. The darkness is always with you.
The darkness.
Despite everything, Yato refused to banish you.
And now it's your turn. Swear on
your name. to always protect him.
Of course. I swear on my name: Yuki.
What's funny?
By the way, Tenjin. I could use
some advice if you've got it to give.
Hmm?
It actually has to do with Hiyori.
Ya see, after her accident, she kinda
slips in and out of her spirit form.
Oh.
The thing is, I accepted her
request to fix it; Which would be fine.
If I knew what in the hell to do!
But I've just kept on putting it off.
I've gotta do it, though. She's
helped me out several times now.
So it's only right! Now's the
time to finally tackle her job!
It's remarkable how much of a lost cause you are.
Have you considered maybe cutting her ties with you?
Huh?
It's just a guess, but doing so
might actually fix her condition.
Wait, cut her ties?
It seems to me that the connection between
you grants her too much of a focus on our world.
Try cutting that connection as a
test. Shouldn't be hard for you.
Studying at the library's so
much better than studying at home.
No kidding.
Another day of solid studying! I'm feeling good!
It can only do so much with the exams we've got
coming. We really need to pick a shrine to pray at.
Yeah! We've gotta pray to a god!
I wish to graduate and be popular and be
healthy and be popular and for my family to be safe!
You wished to be popular twice.
Well, it's that important.
That sure is a lot of wishes. Don't burden the gods.
Isn't it pretty much the gods'
job to hear people's wishes, though?
I mean, why should I care about their schedules?
Right.
Oh, yeah. Speaking of wishes. There's one
god people have been talking about lately.
Oh, yeah, I know.
Wait, which god?
They say that if you tell him the name of someone you
want gone, he'll actually make them disappear for you.
"Lord Rabo, Lord Rabo.
I humbly beg of you!" That's it, right?
That's how it goes.
His name's Rabo?
That's the first I've ever heard of that god.
It's just a dumb fad.
Exactly.
What's with the school books, Hiyori?
Yeah, those are our old ones.
What are you luggin' those around for?
I'm giving them to a friend of mine.
What's up, kids! You workin' hard in here?
Daikoku! I'll take one of those snacks!
What the hell are you doing in our home?
Oh, c'mon, man. Don't be so cold.
This room is for Yukine! Not your lazy ass! Go
suck on some tea leaves if you're hungry! Jeez.
It's still not right. Do it again.
Hiyori. You're kind of strict.
It's easy to mess up this part
and this part. Try to stay focused.
Okay.
Hold on! Let me see. The real trick to
learning. You've gotta draw the stuff!
There! The Pillow Book's Sei Shonagon. Hojoki's
Kamo-no-Chomei. and Tsurezuregusa's Yoshida Kenko.
You're good!
I know, it's impressive. It took work.
But with as long as I've been a god, it ju...
Don't ruin my stuff!
I didn't ruin it! I graced it with my talent!
Why don't you use that talent to earn some money
for a change! Why have you always gotta butt in, huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
What's wrong?
Uh. Nothing. Don't worry about it.
Hiyori! Could you add the black beans to these for me?
Okay!
...has yet to be found. Despite having
taken place in plain sight of others, no...
There've been a lot of stories
about this slasher on the news lately.
I know it's New Year's but...
I wish you'd stay home tonight.
It's just a shrine visit. And
I'll have Yama and Ami with me.
I still can't help but worry.
I can't believe you took a dumb job
like this on New Year's Eve of all nights.
Hey, you gotta take the work when the work comes.
And end-of-year cleaning can be pretty lucrative.
But I've gotta ask.
Does a dog really need its own mansion?
I know, it's huge! Right?
No way! It's even got a heated floor!
Are you serious?
I am so freakin' jealous!
Hello! You have successfully reached
Delivery God Yato. Available 365 days a year.
Yato.
Oh, Hiyori! Hey, what's going on with ya? Hm?
Well uh. Do you wanna come to the Tenjin
shrine tonight for the first visit of the new year?
Huh?
Why d'you wanna visit that geezer? You can't think
of another god to visit tonight? I'm kind of insulted.
Well, I've got my exams coming up.
And you don't even have a shrine to visit.
Guess I'll have to use your wages to buy one!
Are you a god or a pimp?
You don't have to visit the shrine.
There'll be food stalls there too.
Food stalls?
We're in!
Oh, man, I want some candied fruit!
I'll see you guys soon.
All-out, huh?
Hmmm.
Now make sure you don't run in this. You
don't want it to come loose and fall off of you.
I know.
Let's see you.
Oh, you look lovely.
Well, I better go.
Huh.
So that's the half-Phantom deluding Yato.
That's her.
Let's slay her. Reiki.
Not yet.
And why not?
It would be wasteful. She can still be of use to us.
Hiyori!
You got all dressed up for new year.
Yeah! You said "all out"!
We are going all out! I'm
offering a ton of money this year!
We've got the test and a new
school to worry about, and popularity!
Simmer down, dummy. I think it's pretty safe to
say the whole class will move on to the next grade.
Hiyori's playin' it safe with that outfit.
That's not why I'm wearing it!
So... I uh...
I wanted to let you guys know that
someone might join us later. If that's cool.
What? Is it a guy? Is that why you're dressed up?
Hm!
So you're scheming to win his heart by
convincing him you're a different person this year?
Huh, no! I swear it's not like that!
You've got some serious ambition for
the new year. Full blast out of the gate.
Honestly, I'm telling you, it's not like that!
Jeez!
Just drop it already!
Popularity, popularity,
popularity, popularity, please gimme popularity.
Please, please,
please, I just wanna be popular!
Please let me move onto without trouble.
I used to visit shrines just 'cuz I was supposed to,
but now, please let me continue
to have fun with all my new friends.
I want some octopus dumplings.
They look tasty!
Hey, Hiyori. You gonna buy some?
Oh... Mm-hm.
Yato! Wait up!
Hm?
Hiyori! Hey, Hiyori! Wake up!
Her first narcoleptic fit of the year.
Aw, man.
I can't believe we missed ringing in
the new year just to clean a dog mansion.
You have no work ethic! If I get hired to
clean, I'm not leaving until the job is done!
I just hope Hiyori hasn't gotten sick of waiting.
A text? Yeah, it's for another Phantom-slaying job.
Hey, wait, according to the message.
It says to show up right around here.
Come! Sekki!
This is the land of the Rising Sun.
Your desecration shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god Yato. I now lay thee waste with
the Sekki. And expel thy vast defilement! I cleanse thee!
Rend!
Alright. Nicely done, kid.
Hey, thanks.
Huh? We've gotta fight that many?
Stay calm, Yukine. We've got this.
Listen to me. You've really grown a lot,
and you're only gonna keep growing stronger.
You've gotta believe in yourself!
Let me see, Yato. Show me the power of this Regalia.
Display his true worth to you.
Yato?
Are you here?
I'm not picking up his scent around here.
Nora.
Um. Hi, Nora.
Hey, have you seen Yato? I thought
I saw him come this way, but...
What's that? Is it-
I would appreciate it if you wouldn't speak to
me in such a casual manner, you lowly Phantom.
Huh?
Whoa, when did I?
The ablution. I know you played
a large part in the ritual.
You were watching?
That was the perfect chance to
revoke his name. And you squandered it.
Huh?
You're quite fast on your feet, I see.
Go after her Cord. But please
try not to accidentally bite it off.
Why are you attacking me?
You want to know why?
Frankly, because I don't like you.
It's like there's no end to these things!
Yeah, they're persistent to say the least!
They vanished.
How disappointing.
I suppose that's it for my masked ones.
Were you afraid?
Something even more frightening is about to happen.
Huh?
A god of calamity known as Rabo has awoken.
Rabo?
"Lord Rabo, Lord Rabo. I humbly beg of you!"
What about him? If someone wishes for it, Rabo can easily
dispatch the life of a Phantom. Or the life of a person.
Or the life of a god.
A blood-soaked, aberrant god of calamity from the
Far Shore... Rabo has come, and he intends to kill Yato.
No... But... ...But Yato has Yukine with him.
Yato has grown weak from his time spent with you.
If you care about Yato. Then please. Stop existing.
C'mon, come get me!
Alright. You've got 'em all rounded up.
That's right. Now show me the power
of your ragged heart. Let your rage out.
The same rage that drove you to break
those school windows and hurt all you touched!
Fine! Okay! Shut up!
Harness that rage and we'll take 'em out! This is the land
of the Rising Sun. Your desecration shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god Yato. I now lay thee
waste with the Sekki. And expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
And that's all there is to it. Well done.
Now let's go find Hiyori!
Yeah! I can't wait!
Candied fruit! Candied fruit! I'm gonna
buy candied fruit with Hiyori's money...
what the? Don't you owe her enough?
That's it?
That's Yato's strength now?
That's what he's become?
Please don't pass out while walking home, alright?
I'll be okay.
Hiyori!
Hey, happy new year, sorry we're so late.
Happy New Year!
Whoa, hold on. You're not goin' home, are ya?
C'mon, the food stalls are still open, let's go!
It'll be the first food offering of the year!
Unless. You'd rather make your first money offering.
Uh...
Huh?
I um.
Somethin' wrong, Hiyori?
Do we know each other?
Who are you?
What's wrong, Veena? Have you caught a cold-
Actually, it looks like I'm not
the only one sneezing here, Kazuma.
Next time, on Noragami: "Abandoned
God" Huh? Are these hairballs?
Oh, Kuraha must be shedding.