My shrine has grown so neglected.
The world was once ruled by strife
and filled with countless vile wishes.
But the etchings here are those that have been
long since fulfilled, and callers come no more.
Rabo.
And yet... here I stand. Still alive, after all this time.
We two are gods of calamity.
Where we are born from chaos and
suffering, only to be reclaimed by it.
Isn't that so, Yato god?
Huh?
What?
You. Why did you come along with us, you idiot?
Huh? Where are we? How did we get here? And
why do I have a tail? What's going on here?
Oh, man.
I'm pleased you've come.
Rabo.
They seem to have brought one uninvited guest.
I swear... You are nothing but a nuisance.
Hiyori!
Huh?
You need to get far away from here!
Well, here we are.
Come at me!
Sekki!
Reiki!
I will make you return... Hiyori's memories!
We've got him!
You're too slow!
Dammit! I can't break it from the inside!
Furuhime.
The true Yato god has yet to return to us.
Hiyori?
Ow, that hurt.
Hey, are you okay?
Uh-huh. But what the hell are you
doing here? Didn't I tell you to run?
Still. I appreciate it.
Sure.
What is that look on his face?
That thawed, soft expression.
Where is he?
Huh?
The god of calamity I knew!
Where is the true Yato?
Tell me!
With those eyes aflame with beautiful
depravity. Where is that Yato god?
That's the god of calamity
worthy of crossing swords with me!
Shut your mouth!
Now I see.
You don't have the right motivation.
I told you to shut up!
What are you...?
Sekki!
Well Rabo?
I've never seen a Storm this
massive. This does not bode well.
There's no end to them. They just keep coming!
Kazuma.
Yes?
What did Lady Kofuku tell you?
I've got a feeling that a Vent didn't cause this Storm.
You're right, Veena.
A Storm like this. It is the product of a god of calamity.
A god of calamity?
Yukine!
What are we gonna do here, Yato?
I want you to take Hiyori and get away from here.
Huh?
I'm the only one that Rabo's concerned with.
I'll keep him busy while you two get out of here.
What, you can't be serious?
You're completely unarmed without me!
Shut up!
I can handle this.
What is that?
It's the container holding Hiyori's memories.
Huh?
Oh, how tragic.
The mortal life is just too fragile.
Hiyori!
Please! Wake up!
Yato! There's something wrong
with her! Hiyori... What do we do?
Forget the girl, Yato god.
She's been reduced to nothing more than a mindless,
hollow container now. Just an empty sack of flesh.
Rabo.
Have I awakened your hatred?
Finally.
Show me your loathing, fierce deity. Accept and
embrace your maelstrom of hate. God of calamity, Yato!
Be quiet.
Sekki!
There they are. Those are the eyes.
Come!
You come to me this time.
That grin on your face? I'm gonna carve it into a frown.
Yato?
This takes me back.
The sky is roiling above us just as when we lived.
We are gods of calamity.
Fierce deities devoted to heinous wishes and
driven to soak the Near Shore in the blood of innocence.
Enough talk.
This is it.
The moment I've been waiting for.
The moment that my very own wish comes to pass!
My earthly name is Rabo.
Bearing a posthumous name, I don this mask.
And proclaim myself a spirit vessel!
Ye names that assemble cannot defy me.
You are bound and beholden to my every order!
Submit yourselves to me! And obey the mask!
Now gather depravity!
The Storm.
He's absorbing it!
You damn fool. Are you completely
insane? Merging your being with Phantoms?
Insane? Of course not. I've taken this
action... In order to fight you to the death!
Yato! Look! Hiyori!
What's happened to me?
Where am I?
Who am I?
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
This smell.
It seems so familiar.
Yato! You okay? Yato!
Rabo. He's coming for us! Yato! Wake up! Yato!
It smells so nice.
I know I've smelled it somewhere before.
I know it because...
...it's my favorite smell.
Hey why are you crying?
Yato.
You... You know me.
Hiyori!
Huh?
You're okay! You're back! Ha! Hiyori!
Thank you!
Wh-wh-wh-wha?
Get off of me you creepy deadbeat!
She broke my spell completely on her own.
She shouldn't have been able to uncork her memories
How did she?
You cretin! I expected more from you!
Hiyori.
You called me... by my name.
So?
Her memory's back! She knows us!
Well yeah. Why wouldn't I know you guys?
Hiyori!
What will it take to make you return to your old self?
We are gods of calamity! We grant depraved
wishes and feed upon human greed and hate...
So what? Quit bringin' up the
past! It doesn't mean anything now!
Let Hiyori go!
It's all your fault.
You're to blame for his pathetic state!
A pitiful half-Phantom.
You will serve as a sacrifice for my power!
Sekki!
We're taking him out.
Huh?
We'll hit Hiyori from this distance-
It's just like a Borderline.
Rabo's absorbed a Storm and
merged with the Phantoms within.
It's up to you to draw the line
between who gets killed and who survives.
What? It's up to me?
You can do this, Yukine.
We can do this. Together!
This is the land of the rising sun.
Your desecrations shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god Yato.
I now lay thee waste with the Sekki
and expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
Yato!
Hiyori!
You alright?
Let's go home.
Let's go home. Please take me home.
Yato!
Yato.
You have made a wish.
Ya-Yato.
And it's been heard loud and clear.
Yato god!
Yato god.
His face!
Just as I thought.
You used a curse to maintain your disintegrating form.
But why?
It doesn't matter how many wishes we grant them.
People always loathe gods of calamity,
and ultimately, they forget about us.
For better or worse, humans
will always be fickle creatures.
That is the way of things.
It is our inescapable fate to be slain by their disregard.
And so, when I awoke from my 500
year slumber... I yearned to be killed.
Not by the ignorance of man, but by the
hand of one who does truly know me...by you.
You've always been such a downer.
And now, Yato god... I go first. First into the
depths of fate that you and I are bound to share.
Except that I'm nothing like you.
A god has been slain.
Another god lost.
Well, that was a massive failure.
I guess I'd better go home and speak with Father.
So you remember everything? You remember me and Yato?
Yep!
I've gotta ask though. How did you
just suddenly get your memory back?
Huh?
It was because of Yato's... his smell.
His what?
Uh. Never mind, forget it, it's nothing!
Yeah, I don't know how! I can't remember at all!
Okay.
What's up?
Hiyori.
Okay, you're all serious now.
Just listen.
I think it's for the best if you cut all ties with us.
That's the only way you'll really live a happy life.
So.
What? Hey, hold on!
No, I'm not gonna do that.
We're friends. There's no way I'd
be happy without you guys in my life.
Wow! Yatty and Yukki really mean that
much to you? Are you sure about that?
She's just being stubborn for the sake of being stubborn.
That is not true. I mean it. I'm not turning
my back on you. I wanna be with you forever.
You're the only one who wants to cut ties here, Yato.
How romantic!
We need booze!
It's time to celebrate!
Uh, wait! I didn't mean I wanna be with
you forever like that, not in that way!
I'll grant your wish... for five yen.
Pay up!
You've made a wish and it's been heard, loud and clear.
Hiyori Iki. May our fates forever intertwine.