From what I could see, he was ailing badly.
I shouldn't have let him go like that.
Kazuma.
I am here.
Come outside.
Report.
Yes.
Three days have passed since the Vent was opened.
With the help of affiliated and unaffiliated shrines,
we have erected a barrier that has halted its growth.
However, the Phantoms that have already
come out will need to be dealt with.
Have you located Yato yet?
My Lady, I...
Well? Yes?
We're alone here. Speak your mind.
You really shouldn't leave your hair wet like this.
You'll catch cold.
As you wish.
What kind of battle was that, Lady?
You acted on a personal grudge,
without thinking about others.
As a master it was completely irresponsible, Veena.
That's enough.
Dealing with the fallout from
the Vent is our priority now.
It was my fault the damn thing was opened.
I am duty-bound to exterminate those Phantoms.
Prepare to go hunting.
Now that is the lady I follow.
Kuraha! Kinuha! Yugiha!
Akiha! Karuha! Kazuha! Tsuguha!
Let's go!
Yukine?
Are you awake yet?
I brought breakfast, so I hope you're hungry!
Thanks, Hiyori.
Sounds great.
What the...?
What are you doing here, Yato?
You weren't invited! Where's Yukine?
Oh, he ran away.
He's probably over at Tenjin's place.
He ran away, and you didn't stop him?
Why would I? It's not like I need him right now, anyway.
Ah, hello there, dear.
Hi, Lord Tenjin!
Whatever is the matter?
Having school troubles?
I'm sorry. I'm looking for Yukine.
Ah. I saw him. He came by this morning.
I'd like to work for you instead of Yato. Can I do that?
Hm.
So, the new kid only lasted a month, huh?
That doesn't seem like long. How
long were you Lord Yato's Regalia?
Three whole months.
Wow!
I don't know how you did it!
No way I'd be able to.
That sounds impossible.
That's enough, ladies.
It does seem early to have decided you
no longer want Lord Yato as your master.
Is there a specific reason?
I can't stand the guy. Isn't that enough?
He doesn't have a shrine, he's broke,
he's obnoxious, he has a screwed-up past.
And besides, he already has a Regalia.
So, there you go.
Why should I waste time hanging
around with a guy like that?
Hm.
While I'm flattered and delighted you would ask for my
help, I fear it wouldn't be appropriate for me to agree.
You wouldn't want me to give you a name right now, child.
Doing that would make you a Nora, you see.
Nora.
Sorry, but what does that mean, exactly?
Until now I thought it was just someone's name.
How should I explain?
Noras are embarrassing.
Private parts of a god's life, you know.
Get it? Private parts.
Huh?
My lord.
Perhaps you should restrain yourself.
It's only a figure of speech, Tsuyu.
I'm not trying to scandalize the girl!
What is a Nora?
A Nora is a Regalia with many owners.
Not unlike a stray cat, for comparison.
But those who choose to go by many names are seen as
less reliable and more likely to betray their masters.
As such, they are looked down upon, despised.
Think of it his way. What if I offered to become your
godfather? I'll give you a pretty new name and everything.
It'll be fun. I would make a great godparent!
Huh?
Now, what would be a good
name? Yumi, maybe? Or Tomo? Yuko?
Um, thanks a lot, but no.
See? It feels disrespectful, even a bit wrong, doesn't it?
Yeah...
The kind of idea that people instinctively recoil from.
And that's how Noras are seen.
Why they are regarded with such hate.
They're that bad?
Oh, yes. Normally, a Regalia has but
one name and serves only one master.
It is commonly accepted that to serve a new master,
one must first be "unnamed" by the previous master.
Just as Mayu was.
If they're so reviled, why do Noras even exist?
For unsavory tasks.
To put it another way, they're generally used to
perform jobs you wouldn't give to your own Regalias.
Um... Lord Tenjin. I wonder if you
know a girl Nora I met a little while ago.
About the same age as Yukine, I think...
Please, that's enough.
We don't like to talk about Noras.
The very mention of them sends shivers down our spines.
Oh.
Though my lord does seem to speak freely of them.
No need to worry. I've never made
use of one before, nor do I intend to.
I have no wish to entangle myself
with such wretched creatures as Noras.
Don't forget that you can always use me.
Nora.
I've never stopped watching you in all this
time, and yet you never call for me anymore.
I've been so lonely.
That new boy is unstable. You should just get rid of him.
It's not like you don't have options.
I can be useful.
Much more useful than he can.
I've looked all over.
Where is he?
I smell someone, but it isn't Yato.
It's Bishamon!
That confirms it. You can see us.
You're one of Bishamon's people!
And you're that strange living spirit.
The half-Phantom from before.
Yato has many odd acquaintances.
I don't know why I'm surprised.
I'm going to die!
Restraint.
I can't move a single inch.
Umbra.
Okay. Okay.
Maybe a god will come to my rescue.
Aaahh! Yep! I'm totally dead!
Progress? Do you have a location on the next Phantom?
No.
There aren't any here, milady.
Or none that I can smell, anyway.
Kuraha's correct.
We have pretty much cleared out this entire area.
All that remains is the south-southeast region.
Oh?
Wait a sec.
They don't even realize I'm here?
It's a bit soon, but let's try widening the area.
Indeed. I'll catch up with you
once I've conducted one final search.
Very well, then.
I'm sorry, Kuraha. I know your wounds haven't healed yet.
Don't worry, milady. This is nothing.
Look after her. I'll follow soon.
Right!
Interesting.
They're nothing like Lord Tenjin or Kofuku.
They work as one big team. I
didn't know that was possible.
I wouldn't meddle if I were you, Hiyori Iki.
It could be dangerous.
Hey! How do you know what my name is?
And, uh, what did you just do to me?
It's a talent of mine: Manipulating the things around me.
It often comes in handy, given my
line of work. Would you like this back?
Hey! You have my wallet!
But when could you have...?
You should be more careful.
If you cross paths with Bishamon again, keep
your head down, or things could go badly for you.
I still don't understand why you helped me.
I was under the impression you hated Yato.
Make no mistake.
He is certainly our enemy.
However...
I also owe him a great deal.
Speaking of which, is he doing alright?
Huh?
He was blighted. It looked to be pretty severe.
It's that bad?
The blight's source wasn't external.
It most likely came from the inside.
Yato's Regalia.
"Sekki" in that form, right?
It should be disposed of as soon as possible.
What do you mean?
There's nothing to worry about!
Yukine's a good kid. He used to be human!
Isn't killing Regalias like killing people?
It was a long time ago, but Yatty did kill a Regalia once.
He kills people, too, sometimes.
Something must be done before it's too late.
If a Regalia repeatedly does wrong,
its master will fall seriously ill.
If left untreated, the pain will intensify.
The blight will spread throughout
the body, growing ever worse.
Honestly. Why is he even using such a Regalia?
Huh?
You appear to be his close companion.
Has he not mentioned anything about it to you?
Uh, no, he hasn't.
I know this may seem an odd request.
But please look after Yato.
I'd hate to lose him like this.
Right. I'll see what I can do.
Yukine must be dealt with.
If that doesn't happen soon...
Damn it! Stupid, useless old geezer!
Got rejected, did ya?
Shut up!
Well? What do you want?
We got a job. You coming?
Gotta skim the soup.
You call this a job? Are you kidding?
You suck at being a god! Try a temp agency instead!
Quiet, you whiney brat! This is
an honest job for an honest client.
The shop would have to close its
doors without late night help like us!
Oww! Hot! Hot! Hot!
This sucks. Seriously.
Why do I put up with this kinda crap?
Oh, you're actually here.
And so are you.
Hey there, Yatty!
No! Not her!
No gods of poverty wanted here!
You punk!
Think I'll let you touch my lady like that?!
It's justice and you know it!
You two go around tricking people with
that fake name of hers. It's just plain shady!
She uses a trade name! Plenty
of other places do the same thing!
Owie! Rub my boo-boo, Yori. It hurts!
There, poor thing. Does that help?
Hiyori?
How's your latest gig?
We love Yori. She's been so helpful.
She brought us straight to you!
You brought them?
How'd you even know where I was, though?
Um... actually, it's your sm...
Same thing when we asked. She won't cough it up.
"Cough it up"? What are you, a gangster?
Well? Whatcha doin' here?
We got a job that's not our style.
So we were gonna see if you wanted it.
You do want it, don't you?
I guess I could take it.
Hey, uh, you're looking a little pale. How do you feel?
Aw, man. Couldn't afford dinner again?
Yukine.
What'd you do this time?
What?
You don't really think I stole
money, do you? That's messed up.
Oh, come on, man. Even a god's given up on me. Great.
I was better off being dead than working for you.
So Yato was right. You did steal it.
Oh dear. That's bad.
I'll take that job, thanks.
You guys'll stay and look after the shop, right?
Huh?
Wait! Get back here!
That'll be 582 yen, please!
Thanks fer your business, sir.
All it says is to "eliminate the
Phantom that has appeared above Kamiido."
That's a simple enough job.
Yeah. I'll bet branch shrines are getting lots of
these types of requests since the Vent was opened.
Yato.
About Yukine...
I'll find him. Can't do much
Phantom slaying without a Regalia.
That's why you really gotta
keep track of the things, you know?
No. I wasn't asking... I mean, what I wanted...
How do I say this?
I know. I get it.
This problem needs to be put to rest.
It should be disposed of as soon as possible.
Huh?
Whoa! You've finally lost it, haven't you?
Uh...
Yato.
Uh, yeah?
Regalias aren't tools. "Gotta keep track of the things"?
Huh?
Yukine isn't some thing. You
have to treat him like a person.
If you're not willing to do that,
how can you expect him to act like one?
Think about it, okay?
Sure. I will.
You have such pretty eyes for a boy.
They remind me of the fruit on hawthorn plants.
You know.
Not even birds will eat the hawthorn fruit.
Not because of their taste. They aren't
poisonous or anything. They're just empty, is all.
Useless, empty fruit. They offer nothing.
And of course nobody bothers to pick them.
So they're left on the plant to wilt,
wither, and die as pointlessly as they lived.
Poor, lonely little boy.
Yukine!
What are you doing with him, Nora?
You know, Yato. You should really
use me more. Like you used to.
You know I'm good.
I can kill anything in your way with no trouble.
Come on.
Sekki!
Don't listen to anything Nora says. She's vindictive.
Focus on one thing... on that.
Now? Are you sure?
Wait! Yato!
This is the land of the rising sun.
Your desecrations shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god Yato.
I now lay thee waste with the
Sekki and expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
He can't cut through it?
You've gotta be kidding with this!
He's already gotten dull?
All the stings I've gotten
'cause of him. Now there's this?
Smells nice.
Hurry! Get out of there!
Smells nice, nice, nice, nice.
Purification water.
Go, Nora! Just get out of here!
He's a stupid punk with an attitude
problem, but I found him, and I named him.
Sekki! I will re-forge you!
Rend!
They did it!
Rejected you, huh?
So much for his reputation.
He's not the god he used to be.
Let's go.
Yukine must be dealt with.
If that doesn't happen very soon. Then Yato will die.
At this rate, he'll die.
Sorry for decking you like that earlier, man.
Don't worry about it.
Here.
To show there's no hard feelings.
Take it.
Daikoku.
Next time on Noragami: "Over the Line."
Hey, hold on!
This looks like a medical bill!
My lady's got a lump on her head 'cause of you!