I seriously gotta wear this garbage?
Quit yer complainin'.
Here! Check it out! This one's kinda cool.
That's so lame.
Fine, I'll wear it then!
I wonder why I still feel all this physical stuff.
It doesn't make sense,
considering how long I've been dead.
This looks like a good spot to eat.
Eat up.
Is this a joke?
Ya said you were hungry, now didn't ya?
So don't be a snob and eat your lunch.
You call this lunch?
You're my Regalia.
I'm your master and what I say goes!
Your Regalia, huh?
Yup! And I deserve nothin' but
respect from you! Worship me!
You loyally serve your master's every demand!
You could at least serve us some tea, y'know!
With what stove and what tea, exactly?
This backtalk is not gonna fly!
I demand obedience!
You're ripping out my hair!
Get off me, you vicious little monster!
I never would've dreamed this is how a god
lives, drifting around town like some kind of bum,
sleeping out on the stone steps of
some old shrine just to avoid attention,
and digging through garbage
every day just to find some food.
That's your strategy?
Gotta advertise.
For jobs that never come?
Are you positive that you're a real god?
That's rude. You doubt me?
All right, then. I'll show you what I can do.
Welcome. Good afternoon!
Hiyori's offered to buy us some grub
all because she appreciates my services.
This feels like extortion to me.
After you eat, I expect you to
finally take my request seriously.
Hey! Good afternoon.
Can I get you anything to drink?
Yeah, how 'bout two more glasses of water?
Huh?
Oh! I'm so sorry, I didn't see you!
I thought you were invisible to other people,
considering that you're not human and all.
Not quite.
We're not actually invisible.
We're just hard for people to notice, but they can see us.
Let me ask you this.
How many waitresses are working in here?
Huh?
Don't look, that's cheating.
Um, I guess...
Like, two?
Whoa, there's four of them?
And it's the same with us.
Yukine and I just kind of blend in with the
background, just like those other waitresses.
And if someone does notice us,
we look like normal, boring people.
They quickly forget they ever saw us.
I apologize again about that!
Think about it like this.
You don't remember every stranger
you've ever passed on the street, right?
Being from the Far Shore, we're like
the ultimate stranger, so it's stronger.
Well it's pretty noticeable how much food you eat.
Never let an offering go to waste!
An important rule!
You're gonna make yourself sick, you know.
Oh, I'll be fine, gods don't need to poop!
Thank you! Come again!
Jeez! He's really got some nerve!
So, uh, thanks for the food and all.
No problem.
I'm Hiyori Iki, by the way.
You can just call me Hiyori.
So how do you know him, Hiyori?
Um, well...
I kind of sometimes lose my body now,
so I'm hoping he can help me fix that.
Sucks to be you, huh?
I guess so.
Um, so what about you?
How did you, um...
Y'know, what'd you do before you were Yato's Regalia?
Well...
...I dunno. I mean, I do know that I died,
but I can only recall suddenly being in his hand.
And that's all I can remember.
Nothing from when I was alive, and I
don't know what to expect now, either.
Hey, you're that sardine thief from earlier.
Good boy.
He likes you.
Do you like cats?
It seems like it.
Well cats are really cute, huh?
I like them, too.
Yukine... You just had a rather
filthy thought, didn't you?
Listen up, kid, just so you know,
gods and Regalias share mind and body.
So as your master, you subject me
to every one of your pervy thoughts.
Keep our minds out of the gutter!
Huh? I don't even know what you're talking about.
Wait, what do you mean you share mind and body?
Man, you kids.
I know puberty's rough, but try to have a little control.
Shut your mouth, you idiot!
Hey, who do you think you're callin' an idiot?
This is not exactly how I pictured a
wish-granting god to act. Not at all.
Hello! Thanks for calling Delivery God
Yato. I'm fast, affordable, and I get results!
Yukine! We got a job! Let's go!
Someone hired you?
Wait! What about my job?
Hey, what the hell, who invited you along?
You wanna get rid of me?
Finish my job like you said you would!
A tail?
Who are you?
Did you call in a fake job just to set me up?
"When the east wind blows, spread
your fragrance, o plum blossoms."
Plum blossoms?
"Even without your master, do not forget the spring."
Wait, that's a Sugawara-no-Michizane poem.
Don't tell me that's...
...the god of learning!
Lord Tenjin!
Oh, my...
You've heard of me?
Oh, god!
Hey, cut it out!
I'm impressed you recognized the poem, little spirit.
It's a bit of a golden oldie.
It's in all the schoolbooks!
Well, that's distressing.
Don't you have copyright laws?
They expire 50 years after death.
Is that so?
So you're a real god.
Such an impressive aura!
Oh, you flatter me so.
He's the complete opposite.
Hmm? Tell me, Yato.
What's this little one called?
He's called Yuki.
As a Regalia, Sekki, and as a person, he's Yukine.
So, Yukine.
I take it you've only just become a Regalia.
As such, you need not prostrate yourself before me.
Huh?
Tsuyu.
It's true.
To put it simply...
...you already serve in the employ of one god.
And to bow before another, like
so, is to disrespect your master.
Please remember this rule.
Wow!
You've also got like an entire swarm of shrine maidens!
I'm Ayu!
I'm Nayu!
I'm Miyu!
I'm Moyu!
And together we are...
...the maidens of Lord Tenjin!
To be precise, each one of them serves as a Regalia to me.
It can be a task providing for all of them.
Real gods are on a whole different level!
I'm a real god!
So what do you want?
Oh, right, I have my hands full with
requests, it being exam season and all.
So I was hoping you could dispatch some Phantoms for me.
I mean, it's not like you're busy.
And I am aware of the fact that you
sleep in my shrines without permission.
I know you've hit hard times, so I'm more
than happy to let you join my Tenman Group.
I could even make you a branch manager.
But of course, I assume you'd prefer to
have your own shrine. I can respect that.
Oh, I'm sorry, I seem to only have large bills.
Can you make some change?
Oh, how sad. Running a little low on funds, are we?
There's even a class division amongst gods?
That's gotta be why the world's so screwed up.
You had change the whole time?
Now then, I'll provide you with some guidance.
Makoto.
My Lord, Mayu is still new to these parts.
I would suggest another guide.
You do have a point.
This better not be fake.
But Mayu happens to know Yato.
Tomone?
I no longer go by Tomone.
It's Mayu now.
Tomone!
You... You joined this blowhard?
My name is Mayu.
You know each other?
You could say that.
There was a time when I was Yato's Regalia.
Oh, wow! You were, really?
How was it? I mean, working with him?
Did he actually follow through on his jobs?
And what about food and clothing?
Was he always a homeless, jobless, bum in a tracksuit?
Well he would never admit it, but he's actually
every last one of those things you mentioned.
Give your former master some credit here, Tomone!
It's Mayu, dammit!
Quit calling me by that name. It's disrespectful.
You complained nonstop about me putting my hands
on you and now you're some geezer's smoking pipe?
Money sure does change things!
I would have gladly teamed up with anyone but you!
Is she an ex-girlfriend?
No!
An ex-wife, then? You're on pretty bad terms.
It's nothing like that!
Well you sound like a bitter divorced couple.
Excuse me...
This job you need Yato for...
It's to kill Phantoms, right?
Are they really that bad?
I mean, do you have to permanently get rid of them?
Isn't there some other way you can deal with them?
"Disorder on Earth brings disorder to the heavens."
Hiyori, dear, to be honest with you, I can't say
that I approve of the existence of one such as you.
You could too easily complicate
matters without meaning to.
A few days back, Lord Tenjin
received an unsettling wish plaque.
I chose to investigate it, and learned
that two students had taken their own lives.
Why would anybody do that?
This area is plagued by Storms.
The Phantoms they bring cling to
people, and then they take control of them.
Overcome with unbearable heartache,
Lord Michizane erected a barrier here.
Although, people can still carry deeply-rooted inner
demons through it, which hinders the act of purification.
Such an unfortunate waste.
A waste of precious life.
So then all we have to do is the defeat
the Phantoms that are possessing these people?
Yes!
Hiyori?
People are dying because of these Phantoms.
I can't just sit back and let that happen.
If someone wants to die, let 'em die.
Huh?
Spoken like the true scumbag you are.
Y'know, that's a pretty crappy attitude to take.
If a soul's willing to commit
suicide, that means it's been possessed.
It can't even become a Regalia.
Dead or alive, it still doesn't matter.
There's no saving it.
How can you even say that?
Isn't it your job to save people's souls?
Right. I'm out.
Not so fast! You've been paid!
Should we stop her? Or go after her, at least?
Man, why's he gotta be such a jerk?
Yukine...
It's time for your first job.
So what exactly do I have to do?
Come to me when I call for the
Regalia and revert when I call your name.
That's it for now.
Yato...
If someone wants to die, let 'em die.
That's disgusting. You're plain wrong!
Don't wanna get a job.
Don't wanna work, but don't wanna go to college, either.
Sushi Roll Kick!
You're gonna pay for the awful things you make people do!
Is us?
Like us?
One of us?
Your attention please.
A train will be passing Platform 1.
For your safety, please remain behind the yellow line.
She should be with us.
We need her with us.
Come with us.
This way.
Wait!
Jump to me!
You okay?
Man... Try to remember you'll die if your
tail gets cut. Now stay put for a moment.
Yukine... We're barreling
straight towards the real showdown.
I got an E on my practice exam.
Man, this sucks.
E. Z.? Take it easy!
Don't worry, come here and take it easy.
Easy. Easy. Take it easy.
The answer is easy.
We're taking out that Phantom.
Don't wuss out now, all right?
Yeah, no problem.
Easy. Easy.
Oh, no! We're too late!
Relax!
Easy.
This is the land of the Rising Sun.
Your desecrations shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god Yato.
I now lay thee waste with the
Sekki and expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
Yuki! Revert! That's enough! You cut too well!
You said that people who wanna
die should just go ahead and die.
But I guess you don't feel that way after all.
Hate to tell ya, but you're wrong.
I just refuse to let anyone die in front of these guys.
"These guys" who?
I know things can get painful.
But people should still
appreciate what it means to be alive.
If a soul's willing to commit suicide, that means
it's been possessed. It can't even become a Regalia.
The Regalias.
They're all so young and innocent.
And if none of them took their own lives,
then every one of them still wanted to keep on living.
Yato couldn't stand for the Regalias
to see these suicides waste their lives.
He wanted to protect them from that.
Hiyori?
You little perv!
Okay, what'd you do to her?
Nothing!
Hey! I'm okay!
I've just got some debris from
earlier in my eye, that's all!
Huh? That's not okay, it's dangerous!
Huh? No, don't rub them!
Easy!
Listen! Just stay calm!
Take deep breaths, okay?
How's that gonna help?
Use it.
It'll help warm ya up a little.
For your first job, I gotta say that ya
actually did pretty good out there today.
Huh?
Yukine, what's the difference
between butter and margarine?
Uh, their ingredients, right?
Wrong! It's their names! Ha ha!
Are you too slow to solve a simple riddle?
Next time on Noragami: "Where Happiness Lies."
He is so obnoxious.
Hang in there, Yukine.