Rabo.
Reiki.
What the hell is going on here?
Sounds like Yatty and Yukki
have finally made their way home.
Yeah, when exactly did those
two become a part of our household?
This doesn't make sense, what's happening?
Think you could try to calm down? Seriously.
Calm down? But what's wrong with Hiyori?
Uh, Yukine.
This guy you're with...
Who is he?
What do you mean?
Nice one, Hiyori, now quit jokin'
around. C'mon, it's me, ya dummy!
Meyadummy... That's your name?
Yeah! Mister Meyadummy! That's'a me!
Well that was a stupid accent!
So, Yukine? He's a friend of
yours? Is he a comedian or something?
Huh?
It's gotta be some form of amnesia.
It must be!
The really weird thing about it is that the
only thing she seems to have forgotten is you.
What do we do?
For starters, quit freaking out. I bet it's just a
temporary condition. I'm sure she'll remember you soon.
No.
No what?
I will make Hiyori normal again.
That's it!
Follow me this way!
I was actually just dropping by to give
you these old reference books to study.
I know, but just humor him, will ya?
If I can direct your attention to the
left. This street! This famous street.
This is the very location where the god
Yato met a certain girl while rescuing Milord!
Huh?
A lord used to live around here? That's cool. I
had no idea there was so much history to this street.
I don't think that's jogging her memory.
Do you know his name, Mr. Yato? The lord.
"Mr. Yato"? It's Yato! There's
no "mister"! You only call me Yato!
Okay. It just seems kind of
rude to call you that right away.
I'll show you, Hiyori!
Hey! Quit drawing in my books!
This is Milord! He's a cat!
Oh, wow.
That's great! You're talented, Mr. Yato.
I'm trying to show you the drawing, not my artistry!
Oh, that's right.
Milord was the name of the cat that you drew.
You remember the cat? So, do you remember me then?
Let me think.
You're a manga artist?
I'm sorry, but I really need to get going.
Do you mind if we do your lessons another time, Yukine?
I've put your homework assignments
in here until we can meet.
Sure. Thanks.
See ya.
Wait!
Please, Hiyori.
Do you really not remember me?
Just try to think. Is there nothing there?
In that case...
Let's get into bed together. That just might
help you remember when we met at the hospital...
Pervert!
Yatty and Yukki wanted us
to put some dinner aside for them to eat later.
Right. Meals are the one thing they never seem to miss.
A picture book of her memories?
After everything else, you really think that's gonna work?
Yes! It will! You saw how she reacted earlier! The
drawing of Milord clearly woke something inside her!
Now quit naysaying and help me here!
Whatever. You can make your own coloring book.
It's weird. That guy seemed so desperate.
I wonder why it's so important to him.
Alright! I've got all the tools for a
vivid picture book! It won't be long now!
Man, I can't believe you threw away what
little money you had on some stupid art supplies.
Anything for the sake of Hiyori!
Now that I think about it. Maybe
something specific caused this.
Yato?
What's wrong?
I should have known you were somehow behind this. Nora.
Behind what, Yato? Erasing Hiyori's memories of you?
It was actually rather easy. There's no reason for her to
retain memories of Far Shore denizens in her simple mind.
It seems that people are
quick to forget that they've ever met you.
Wouldn't you agree?
No matter how much you grant humans' wishes,
their behavior is always so fickle and erratic.
Poor Yato, don't you ever get tired of being hurt so much?
Why keep putting yourself through it? Wouldn't
it be easier to simply embrace your true self?
Yato! Snap out of it! Don't let her mess with your head!
You're right.
Fine, Nora, just what the hell are you scheming this time?
I only wanted to get your attention to
make sure that you haven't forgotten us, Yato.
Reiki.
You... It can't be... Rabo!
How are you alive?
It's been a long time, Yato god.
Who is he?
That's a cute sun visor you're wearing.
Let's begin.
Come. Sekki!
Whoa! You actually wanna kill this guy?
If I hold back even a little bit he'll kill me right away.
Damn! He's as fast as always!
Yato god.
What has become of you?
This is not the power of the god I once knew.
You must remember.
You must remember...
You must remember!
Yato!
Yato, are you okay?
As for the next report...
What is this?
What's happening?
Yato.
Yukine!
There's no doubt. The Yato god
I knew is a thing of the past.
Furuhime.
I know, but now you see.
Listen, Yato.
I'd like to see you defeat Rabo. If you
do. I'll return Hiyori Iki's memory to her.
And that's a promise.
So, as far as this sudden storm goes? Nope.
I'm afraid my lady's got nothin' to do with it.
You're the first god I come to when a Vent randomly opens.
I never would've thought Yato was involved.
It was brutal. We couldn't even come
close to taking down this Rabo guy.
Rabo, huh?
I've never heard of the dude.
A god of calamity.
Nobody has spoken his name in ages now.
But he was apparently well-known long ago.
Then you know him, master?
Rabo was in fact originally human. As I
recall, in his life, he served as a Herald.
What's a Herald?
A minion who sneaks into enemy land.
A thug who carries out dirty work.
Once a Herald finishes his work, his
master kills him to ensure his silence.
Seriously?
Apparently. He was deified after he was
murdered, and turned into a god of calamity.
Wait, what's a god of calamity?
People don't always ask the gods
for good things. There are bad wishes.
Really? Like what?
The destruction of someone you hate, for example.
A god of calamity hears these
wicked requests, and fulfills them.
Rabo favored senseless murder as his
particular method in granting these wishes.
There's no discernment to his actions.
He kills Phantoms. He kills humans.
And he's even been known to kill gods.
On request.
Wha...?
What does someone like that want with Hiyori?
I'm guessing he's an old pal of Yato's?
I have heard certain rumors.
Yato did allegedly partner with a god of calamity.
Rabo hasn't changed at all. He's just as powerful.
If I'm not careful, he might kill Yukine.
How is he? Shouldn't simply existing be
a struggle for a god of calamity like him?
What? Hold on a minute! You're telling
me that those two worked together?
Does that mean...? Is Yato a god of calamity too?
I didn't even know...
Yori knows something about it.
I mentioned it to her once before.
That's right. And she didn't seem
to have any problems with it, either.
That girl. She's one tough cookie, ya know?
Yatty's different than he used to be.
Which is why Yori's stuck by his side.
I think it's pretty obvious at this point
that Yori really loves you and Yatty.
I... I have to get her memories back for her.
She'll never remember me. Not at this rate.
Perhaps it's for the best if she doesn't.
As I've said before, you should cut your ties with her.
Your connection gives her too much of a
direct focus on the events of our world.
It will eventually keep her from living in her own.
Forgetting you could be the best thing to happen to her.
She'll likely revert back to her fully human state.
And she'll never be happy as a half-Phantom.
He appears to have made up his mind.
Poor Yato.
Yato! Where have you been all night?
Listen to this. I was thinking about Hiyori's mem...
Forget it.
Just forget about Hiyori.
What? Hey! Yato! Yato!
We must act quickly.
The longer we wait, the more
remorseless the passage of time becomes.
You worry too much.
Yato will return very soon.
I'm sure of it.
And then!
Yukki! Have you seen Yatty yet?
What the hell?
What's wrong with Yato now?
This doesn't make sense.
Why now?
I drew this.
But how?
The only way I could have is if I do know him.
But if I do, why can't I remember him?
It's Yukine.
Hiyori!
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
No big. So what's up?
For you.
Wow, a picture book!
So did you make it?
Can I read it to you?
Uh-huh.
Here we go.
This is the story of Yato,
the tracksuit-wearing god and his friend Hiyori.
Now let the tale begin!
Dammit, Yukine. He's with Hiyori again.
And on his very first try, the
gifted Regalia drew a Borderline.
That's so cool! You really are amazing, Yukine.
Even Yato was surprised when I did it.
Really? He was?
Uh, yeah. Moving on.
Yato.
Do you recognize this?
So the ablution was a success.
All thanks to Yato and Hiyori.
If neither of you had been there for me.
Then I might not have been able to come back.
And that's how...
That's how...
And that's how Hiyori, Yato, and
I... ...all became best friends.
I'm sorry, but I still don't have
any memories of Mr. Yato.
Although, it does sound like we really are good friends.
Yeah!
So, I was wondering.
If you don't mind and all, could I have that book?
Huh? Uh, y'see, the thing...
I just kind of feel like if I keep looking at it over
and over, it might help me remember what I've forgotten.
If you think so.
The lunar cycle is waning.
Tell me, Yato. Where do you suppose
the waning part of the moon goes?
Where does it go?
You okay?
Hiyori...
Um. Is this yours?
Yukine.
What the hell have you done, Nora?
Hiyori's memory is waning bit by
bit, falling away into total darkness.
If you don't come see us, and soon,
she'll end up as nothing but an empty vessel.
Hiyori.
She's forgotten about me now.
She doesn't remember me!
Yukine.
We're going to get her memory back. It's just...
Going up against them again could very likely destroy you.
Yato.
Not only that, but I might
give them exactly what they want.
You have to believe in yourself.
That is what you told me, right?
Is that supposed to be me?
Why do I have a tail?
Hiyori! Time to go!
Hiyori!
Uh, yeah?
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
freaked out on you like that earlier.
Really. You're the one who's
being tormented through all this.
The thing is. We've dragged you into something terrible.
Actually. It's Yato's crappy history that's to blame here.
But, he is still my master, and his
problems are, well they're my problems, too.
Do I have to do all the talking?
I promise that we will get your memory back,
so you just rest easy and wait. Okay?
Hiyori? What's wrong?
I'm actually not sure. I don't know why I'm crying.
Enough of that.
Let's go.
Dun-duh-dun! It's time for your Regalia
midterms! List ten good things about me!
Ten?
You're already failing! Try for five.
Five?
Next time on Noragami: "A Scrap of a Memory."
Fine, just the best three!
I'm sorry, but I can't think of any.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Are you serious?