Help us!
Please! Yato needs you!
Ya...
Border!
A Borderline?
Take it down! Please let us in! Daikoku! Kofuku!
Don't just stand there! Can't you see?
Yato's going to die!
You're the only one I'm letting inside.
Kofuku. Can you purify Hiyori and cleanse her blight?
Right.
This water's pure. It's pumped in directly from the
spring in the garden. Come over here and wash your body.
What about Yato?
It's too late for Yatty's blight to be cleansed now.
It can't be! How?
Yuki...
He needs to be punished.
Kofuku. Take over for a while.
I'm gonna visit some nearby shrines.
What?
Why do you need to do that?
What is Yukine's punishment?
He needs ablution.
Huh?
An ablution's a ceremony for expelling blight.
But it requires three Regalias to pull it off.
So we'll need two more besides me.
Just to be clear here. You know what'll
happen if the ablution fails. You do, right?
Yeah.
Regardless... We need the other Regalias here right away.
He doesn't look like he'll even last until the morning.
Yukine.
Take one step from where you're
standing and I will kill you.
Yeah, whatever.
That's cold!
Yato is seriously on the verge of death.
But what exactly are they going to do to punish Yukine?
Please. Please, please. Just let them both be
okay. Actually... I never really thought about it but,
Who does help gods and Regalias?
Yato's truly dying?
Yes.
An actual ablution?
If you don't do it correctly,
you can get eaten by a Phantom.
What? Are you serious?
I had a friend who took part in one.
It was a serious ablution and she helped out.
What happened to her?
Is she okay?
I don't know.
Nobody has seen her since it took place.
If you'll permit it. I can help.
Hey, hold on! You aren't serious, are you?
Yato did grant me the name Tomo at one time.
Thank you. And who are...?
Mayu, now.
We only need one more, then.
I greatly appreciate your assistance. I
ask no more. You've been generous enough.
Please try not to fret over this. Worrying
would only affect Lord Tenjin's health.
My Lord.
Yato's been corrupted. How could
that fool allow this? What is he doing?
Please hear me out.
Would you kindly allow me to borrow one Regalia?
I humbly beg of you.
Please!
When corruption has already set in.
There's no guarantee that
using Regalias can save a master.
What kind of Regalia inflicts this
much upon its master in the first place?
You must slay Yukine, Yato.
Daikoku! Yeah okay... what?
You could only find one Regalia?
What are we gonna do, Daikoku?
Keep looking. That's the only thing I can do.
Yeah. I-I know. Mm, right. I'll call you back later
with an update. The only other gods around here are...
We've gotta do something. If we can't find
someone else to help us, Yatty's gonna die.
Just one more! I need to find one more Regalia.
There's always Nora. I'm certain she'd come to Yato's aid.
Except, what would be the cost?
You know I'm good. I can kill
anything in your way with no trouble.
She just might kill Yukine. In that case.
You should be more careful.
If you cross paths with Bishamon again, keep
your head down, or things could go badly for you.
This is no time to be afraid.
Come out, Kazuma! I need your help! Please, Kazuma!
Has there been activity in the northeast?
It's all fairly quiet. There are no
signs of any vent openings for now.
And in the southeast?
All clear... Nothing to report.
I'll continue to remain alert though.
I'm really sorry, Kazuma, but well...
Hm?
A girl's been calling for you
outside a shrine for a while now.
What is it? Well?
Sorry it's nothing.
This girl's too ill-mannered
to even offer a bow. Ignore her.
Okay.
Now then. Let's get back to your reports.
Please, Kazuma! You have to talk
to me! Please, I need your help!
We're talking life and death here, Kazuma! Plea...
You couldn't find one more person! You dummy, what's
wrong with you? You didn't even try looking, did you?
Of course I looked! But no one is willing to take the risk
to help the Regalia of a god they've never even heard of.
Please try to hang in there. We're trying. Please, Yato!
Didn't I tell you not to move?
Do I look like I care?
And where are you going?
Kazuma?
Who is that?
How's Yato holding up?
Hold on, isn't Yato your master's sworn enemy?
He is. But I personally owe him a debt.
On top of that. She came to me for help.
Yori?
I suggest you give her a stern lecture. I've
warned her myself, yet she came right to our front door.
Veena would've killed her if she had known.
Well, I don't know what kind of debt you
owe him, but we've got our three Regalias now.
You do. But the state he's in?
This is not going to be easy.
Yato. Can you hear me? You need to banish
Yukine. You can't endure this for much longer.
Yato!
He just won't listen to reason.
That's why an ablution is the only way we can save him.
Yukine. What'd you do?
I don't know. Nothing.
If that's true, then why were you just trying to leave?
'Cuz I wanted to, okay?
Or maybe it's because you can't handle the guilt you feel.
Or it's because I'm sick and tired of all
of you! I said I didn't do anything, alright?
Is that so? Then you wouldn't
mind taking off your shirt for a sec.
Uh, what? Why should I?
Just shut up and do what I say.
What is that?
Damn it! You stung your master that much?
Are you ready to do this?
Yes.
Hurry and get it off me! Please, just get it off!
We now cleanse this spirit belonging to the god
Yato, and we preserve the name with which it was graced.
What is this?
With defilement expelled and avarice removed. We
bring forth a sincere, principled, and just soul.
With flesh pared may he be cleansed.
What're they?
An ablution involves purifying the flesh through burning.
They're using the Regalia borderlines
to hold him in place and cleanse him.
They're doing... what?
They all used to be human. Only Regalias
may judge the sins of other Regalias.
Stop it! Let me out, damn it!
And once an ablution has officially
begun, it's not safe to stop until it's over.
Not until the Regalia has confessed and
repented all of their sins. Every last one of them.
Yukine! Confess your evils! Do it now!
Shut up! I'll kill you for this!
But if he refuses...
Harder! He's becoming a phantom!
Stop watching!
This is cruel! You have to stop them! He can't take it!
I didn't do anything to deserve this! Why
the hell are you putting me through this?
I didn't do anything wrong!
All of this just 'cuz of some loose change?
So I stole some stuff, and I broke some
stuff! Who freaking cares? I didn't hurt anyone!
Don't act like you don't understand
me! It's because we're dead!
But they're not! They have everything!
And they don't even appreciate it!
My folks are really pissing me off.
I had my brother help me.
C'mon! We're your friends!
A future, memories, a family and friends...
They get to have everything.
Everything that's been taken from me.
They've got it all and I have nothing!
It's not fair.
I'm completely alone.
And I have nothing.
Nothing at all.
You have such pretty eyes for a boy. They
remind me of the fruit on hawthorn plants.
You know.
Not even birds will eat the hawthorn fruit.
Not because of their taste. They aren't
poisonous or anything. They're just empty is all.
Useless, empty fruit. They offer nothing.
And of course nobody bothers to pick them.
So they're left on the plant to wilt, wither, and die.
and die...
Poor, lonely little boy.
So what if I stole a few things? And why does it matter
if I smashed up some stuff? Everyone should be like me.
They should be like me and die!
It's just no use! He's fighting too much!
Daikoku! Change into the Kokki and slay him!
Keep your cool, you mousy dumbass!
It'll collapse if I transform now! And
besides. I'd just open up a vent in my Kokki form.
Now quit freakin' out and try to think clearly!
Look!
If his mark gets enveloped, we're screwed!
Don't you give up now!
His name. I need to say it. I need to call his name.
Before it disappears.
When I picked him, I had a feeling
he was more than a pretty face.
Isn't that right, Yukine?
I can't let him cross to the other side.
I need to call his name.
Yukine!
Yori, No!
Hey! Get away! It's too dangerous!
Yukine! Don't cross to the other side!
You can't let yourself become a Phantom!
Listen to me, Yukine! Yato is still here for you!
I know you know that's true! I know you heard him!
He's a stupid punk with an attitude
problem, but I found him, and I named him.
Sekki! I will re-forge you!
That's what he said. He cares about you like a father!
Think about it. Even when you kept on
betraying Yato and hurting him, he just endured it!
But if you keep hurting someone who's that good
to you, Then I... can't be friends with you anymore!
Friends...
You're my friend?
Yukine!
I know it's hard, and it's not
fair. You can't be with people anymore.
I'm sorry that you're no longer like them.
But, Yukine... I granted you the name of a person!
So...
You can still live as a person! You can live, Yukine!
Yato...
I'm so...
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry! I kept on stinging Yato! I
stole money! And Hiyori. I... I tried to feel her up!
I stole the skateboard, too. And I smashed
out all the windows! And I told so many lies!
I won't do it anymore!
I promise!
I'm really sorry for everything!
I'm sorry!
Okay! There's no blight to be found!
I thought I was a dead man.
But you are dead.
Why does punishment gotta be so exhausting?
I wanna thank you guys for helping
out this dimwit. I appreciate it.
I would hope you do.
You too, Hiyori. I never thought
it'd cause you this much trouble.
Yukine.
Come here, buddy.
I'm sorry! Now you tell her, too!
Hiyori. I'm sorry!
Hiyori.
If she hadn't thought to bring us here.
I'm sure I would've died where I was.
Also, if she had chosen Nora as one of the Regalias.
Well, the pain was so intense, I might
have been tempted to use Nora to end it.
And of course, if she hadn't stopped Yukine when she did...
If she... hadn't been by my side.
She saved us.
She made every right move and saved us.
I'm so relieved! I'm so glad you're both okay!
I'm so... I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
The stew has now started to
bubble. Is it ready to eat?
I'll taste it and see for
myself. Munch, munch, munch.
I really thought the Phantoms were
gonna munch him up for sure back there.
Well, now I know that waking you
up was the right choice after all.
Rabo.
The stew has now started to bubble. Is it
ready to eat? I'll taste it and see for myself.
It is ready.
Yato.
Is he truly the former god of calamity?
The Yato?
I suppose you'll just have to find out for yourself.
Next time, on Noragami: "Regarded with Hate."
So, it's nice to meet you. I'm Mayu.
Oh, yeah, my name. I'm Daikoku.
I'm Kazuma. Sorry, but I've gotta go now.
Same here.
Uh... Sure.
Later.
Man, those two are surprisingly alike.