[LOU] What he meant was,
we have to stay here.
[EMILICO] We have no choice,
the door's been locked.
[SHAUN] I don't really
understand the criteria.
He's definitely watching us
to see how we fulfill our role
as a shadow face.
But I can't figure out why
Ricky was demoted one rank.
Not to mention your demotion.
Who knows what that...
[RICKY] Enough, already!
Well, we weren't
actually told to dance.
What?! So I took the initiative
and now it's my fault?
Listen, you all danced, too,
so you're just as guilty!
I guess we'll see.
I have a feeling it's
at the whim of Edward.
[RICKY]
But that's so unfair!
You musn't forget...
We're living dolls.
The Shadows family may
treat us however they see fit.
Aren't you just fretting over
trivial matters now, Ricky?
Oh, that's rich!
You're one to talk!
[SHAUN] Where are they?
It's been too long.
The Garden Maze
I wonder if we're
supposed to go, too?
Don't be stupid. It's locked,
and he told us not to come.
Just a thought,
but try using your brain.
Are you even capable
of that, Black Sheep?
What do you mean? He never
said we shouldn't follow!
[RICKY] Maybe not, but that's
what he meant and you...
[inaudible]
[EMILICO]
Please don't fight, you two!
[RICKY] Huh? Ah,
now I understand why
they call you "Miss Sunshine."
We're rivals, That's what we do.
You holding your cup
like that is the real tragedy.
[EMILICO gasps]
[RICKY]
I feel sorry for Kate.
You're supposed to hold
a teacup by the handle,
that's why it's there.
Elegant, right?
[chuckles]
Absolutely no one holds
their teacup in both hands.
Ah! Ricky!
That's so kind of you!
Thank you for telling me!
Ah!
[growls]
Don't you do that!
You're nothing but an unloved
doll with a freakish name!
[gasps]
But Mistress Kate... she told me
I was fine just the way I am.
And I have no right or reason
not to believe her.
Ahh... Mm!
Mm, ahh!
[RICKY growls]
[SHAUN gasps]
[gasps]
That is so disgusting!
You're trying to
mock me now, aren't you?
[gasps]
A stone?
You little fool!
That's what you get for thinking
it was okay to go ahead
and eat that food.
Another helping
of Edward's abuse.
Wait... I've seen this,
but where?
Oh, a fève. I read about them.
It's a small porcelain
good luck charm.
One is placed inside galette
des rois, a sweet pastry eaten
on New Years', and happiness
comes to whoever finds it.
Great! And how is
that useless knowledge
supposed to help us
in the debut?!
[EMILICO]
There's a bit of writing on it.
Edward did tell us we should
eat our sweets, remember?
[SHAUN]
That's right, he did, didn't he?
Maybe there are more
fèves hidden inside.
They might spell out
a message or something.
Nice work, Emilico!
Come on, let's eat!
That's a lot of food
for five of us.
[RICKY]
I'm not eating all of that.
Your "theory" is
just a wild guess.
[SHAUN] Good for you,
if you think you know better.
But don't come crying
if your rating goes down.
[RICKY growls]
[SHAUN] "There is a good luck
charm in the galette des rois."
Is that a clue?
Seriously?
[SHAUN] I don't understand what
we're supposed to do with that.
[RICKY]
Damn it! See?!
I knew this was just
more of his abuse!
[groans]
[RICKY]
I... ate too much.
I feel sick.
[grunts]
[EMILICO gasps]
[SHAUN]
Hmm?
E-Emilico?
[gasping]
Look, it worked!
So, that means... we should
definitely go after them, right?
It could be a trap, you know.
Besides, we're not even sure
if those really are fèves.
Why should we risk
our own safety?
[EMILICO]
Come on, let's go!
After all, worrying
about our masters...
That's certainly not
a "trivial matter"!
[SHAUN gasps]
[RUM]
Mm!
[EDWARD]
It was supposed to be easy.
Kate can be brought down...
No, must be brought down.
But I got her
living doll all fired up.
Worse than that, when
I played piano to calm myself,
Patrick and his stupid doll
got the grand idea
to start dancing around!
Now Kate and her doll
seem closer,
which makes them even
harder to eliminate!
The truth is, this debut is
a test of my skill as a judge.
If no one fails, I'll seem less
than motivated to do my job.
But I can't simply fail
a pair without good reason.
I must find a way to get
my plan back on track!
Calm yourself, Edward.
It really isn't that difficult.
[EDWARD] That took even longer
than I'd thought.
Aren't you forgetting something
kind of important, here?
Please tell us
where our masters are.
The rules are fairly simple.
Obviously, you must
exit the garden
before the allotted
time expires.
But first, you must
save your masters.
What have you done to them that
they would need rescuing from?
[EDWARD]
Of course you're concerned.
It's important
you feel that way.
After all, living dolls exist
for the sake of their masters.
Why is it even necessary
for you to put us
through this whole thing?!
Such questions are trivial.
Immaterial! Do remember:
You must carefully consider what
you should and shouldn't allow
into your thoughts.
Protecting your masters comes
first, for they are nobles.
In addition, no harm must
come to a living doll's face
while in the labyrinth.
And a shadow's attire
must not get dirty.
Thus far, the ranking from
the top down is Lou, Shaun,
Ricky, Rum, and last, Emilico.
Higher rankings give you
a greater advantage.
All of the items you see
over there may prove useful
to complete this challenge.
The top-ranked doll
will choose first.
[RICKY chuckles] What kind of
dumb idiot would choose a rock
over one of those other things?
I'll take this one.
That's how you make choices?!
Yes. Decisions are hard for me.
[RICKY]
Sure, but you can't avoid them.
It's not like you have the
capacity for regret, anyway.
[RICKY] Carrying junk around
isn't really my style.
What is, though?
There could definitely be
trouble if she threatens me
with those shears.
Should I choose that
as a weapon?
[SHAUN] I'm gonna need
something really versatile.
Water... Does that mean
we might have to deal
with scorches out here?
[SHAUN] Bread... So,
this won't be over today?
We're in for a long haul?
[EDWARD] Hurry up and choose.
You two are ranked the same.
I'll let you decide between you
who gets to pick first.
All right, in that case,
I'll go ahead.
[RICKY]
Like hell you will!
Lotta nerve you've got!
[grunts]
Listen, buddy. You had better
stop messing with me, or else.
You already punched me once,
so it's not like you're taking
the high ground here.
Shall we pick up
where we left off?
Hey, guys? I know,
why not both say
what you want to choose
at the same time?
[BOTH]
There's only one choice!
Magnifying glass!
The soot suit, of course!
[BOTH growl]
[EMILICO] Wonderful!
See how it worked out?
[EDWARD]
Next, we have Rum.
[RUM]
Uh... Uh.
[RICKY chuckles]
A lantern during the day?
That's real smart.
[RUM whimpers softly]
You may talk tough, but when
it came right down to it,
you chose something
to protect yourself.
[RICKY] Well, yeah,
didn't you hear the rules?
No harm must come to
a living doll's face.
And last, Emilico.
Hurray for me!
What I want's still there!
Come on, that's a lie.
There's only junk left now!
What are you talking about?!
Do you not see that bread?
How are you even thinking
about food after everything
we just ate?
[RUM, SHAUN]
Bread. No surprise.
My apologies, bread.
Not this time, I'm afraid.
That is what I was hoping for!
[RICKY] Hmm? Oh, wow,
she's an even bigger idiot
than I thought!
Emilico, why pick that?
It looks heavy.
Maybe so, but I had to have it!
Heh.
It takes approximately
two hours for the soot to go
from bottom to top
in the sootglass.
You must bring your master to
the exit before that happens.
Take this and wait at
the entrance
I told each of you to go to.
[EDWARD]
Now... begin!
[SHAUN] A pencil, rope,
scissors, a handkerchief,
and a map.
[SHAUN] This shape
looks like a small hut.
[SHAUN grunts]
What is this black dot?
[SHAUN] Oh, five, total. Is that
where the shadow masters are?
[groans]
[SHAUN]
Writing, maybe...?
Must be a hint!
The magnifying glass was smart!
Maybe I can use it to pinpoint
my master's location.
[SHAUN]
I can't read it, even with this.
But, Emilico...
Her eyes are sharper than mine.
[EMILICO]
Hmm...
Ah! Rum, hi!
Fancy meeting you here!
Just a little joke. My entrance
was right next to yours, so...
I thought I might run into
you if I came this way.
[RUMMY]
Me, too.
[gasps] So, have you
decided where to go?
[RUM gasps]
Mm.
Well, look at this, I'm heading
for this little hut mark nearby.
We should go together!
[gasps]
I'll be right back.
[EMILICO gasps]
There's water below!
[EMILICO] I must pay more
attention. I nearly fell in.
Let's add the waterway
to the map.
This is kind of fun,
don't you think?
[RICKY] Tsk. Guess I could've
used that lantern after all.
[RICKY]
Hmm?
[wings flapping]
[RICKY]
Hmm...
[RICKY gasps, grunts]
[RICKY screams]
Hush, now.
[RICKY]
Are you kidding?!
You made a shortcut
through the hedge?
I didn't even know
that was allowed!
[RICKY] Hold on... I might be
able to use her to my advantage.
[RICKY] Tell me, Lou,
where are you headed?
Nowhere special.
[RICKY] You know,
your utter lack of thought
is actually impressive.
By the way, I think I know where
the shadow masters are.
[LOU] No, you don't.
[RICKY] Oh, yes, I do, too!
There's a hint right on the map.
[LOU]
What map?
[RICKY] The one inside
the bag we all got!
The map has these little dots
that seem like nothing,
but they're not, and I'm
the only one who noticed!
Tell you what,
I'll make you a deal.
I'll take you there with me
if you hack us a shortcut.
[LOU]
Okay, tell me where to start.
[RICKY]
Hmm.
[LOU]
However...
If you're lying, I'll be forced
to give you a buzz cut.
Uh. A-All right,
you've got a deal.
[RUM whimpers]
[EMILICO gasps]
You can feel free to put your
stuff in here if you'd like.
Oh, I, um...
Go ahead!
[EMILICO grunting]
Don't worry, I'm fine! See?
I can even push it
with one hand.
[yelps]
[screams]
[EMILICO whimpers]
Oh. That was pretty scary!
But at least it stopped.
[sighs]
Ah. No, really,
I don't need any help.
[gasps]
[EMILICO]
That was my own silly fault.
[EMILICO sighs]
All right!
Huh?
[RUM]
Please, I want to help.
I know we can push it up
if we work together.
[gasps]
[EMILICO] I guess...
I was trying to be strong.
Hmm!
[RUM grunts]
Ah. You were so right!
We can get more done
when we work together!
[BOTH grunting]
[grunting]
[EMILICO sighs]
We made it!
[RUM sighs]
I'm so proud of us!
[boom]
[BOTH gasp]
An explosion?!
Did someone trigger
a trap or something?
[JOHN] Soot really packs
a punch, who knew?
[JOHN grunts]
[sighs]
[JOHN]
Ah, the air is so refreshing!
A stroll might be nice.
[EMILICO]
Ah!
This place is huge!
You can see all sorts of
amazing things from up here!
[EMILICO gasps]
Is that... soot?
[inaudible]
[EMILICO] There are little black
dots on the map there, too.
That's it!
The dots represent
the shadow masters!
And see, one of them
is even nearby!
Let's go have a look!
[EMILICO] Ah! Surely,
it can't hurt to stop and pick
a few more oranges
for Mistress Kate!
[KATE] Well, Edward said to wait
here till someone comes, but...
[KATE] Maybe this soot power
could help with that.
[KATE] Or is it too risky
to draw attention that way?
It's just so tempting, though.
[JOHN]
Oh, it's you, Kate!
That's quite
an interesting spot.
[KATE]
John!
[JOHN]
This is perfect.
There's a question
that cannot wait.
John wants your hand
in marriage!
[KATE]
No chance.
[JOHN]
Don't be so hasty!
John has taken a fancy to you.
And just think, he shall
be King of Shadows House!
You would never
regret your choice.
[KATE]
What's with him? Is he a fool?
[KATE] Are you saying
you'll only help me
if we're to be married?
Kate will not marry someone
as calculating as that.
Well done. Yes, indeed,
that was my plan.
Quite perceptive.
You are the one for John.
[KATE]
Why won't he go away already?
[JOHN] John was put in a crate,
but with a wham, bang, kaboom...
He blew it to bits and escaped
like the true hero he is!
If you overcome this ordeal on
your own, we'll be equals.
Then, we may revisit
the subject.
[KATE] Wait. So then,
Shaun didn't help you escape?
[JOHN] No. John did it without
anyone else's help, thank you.
[KATE]
But how?
[JOHN] Weren't you listening?!
It was like, wham, bang, kaboom!
[KATE] It appears he wasn't
consciously controlling
the soot, then.
[JOHN]
But in your case...
[KATE gasps]
[JOHN] That cage really
is quite a sight to see.
It looks more challenging
than John's crate.
[KATE] How will Shaun be
able to find you if you're not
where you should be, anyway?
[JOHN]
Oh, right, we were told to wait.
Shaun was meant to come?
I suppose that makes sense.
You're a smart one, Kate.
Goodbye for now!
Call loudly for John if you
decide you'd like to be saved.
[KATE] So, there were
no repercussions
for his conspicuous use of soot.
That's good to know.
It's also quite helpful knowing
there are other shadows
who can control soot besides me.
[KATE] This whole test feels
like a giant spectacle.
[KATE]
The debut...
It's as if... someone
was watching us.
[JOSEPH] It appears John
has failed in his efforts
to throw Kate off-kilter.
[SOPHIE]
That may be so, but still,
his high soot volume
was quite impressive.
Epic failures are
more entertaining than
outstanding candidates.
[JOSEPH]
Ryan, what vulgar taste.
This is a test.
[DOROTHY]
Oh, please.
It's one of the few diversions
we have in this place!
And I must say, both John and
that labyrinth-chopping doll
are most entertaining.
Though, Edward did go through
such pains to create it,
poor fellow.
[RYAN] Why, does he mean
to be a gardener?
His obstinate
personality's on display.
[JOSEPH]
"Earnest" is more accurate.
[SOPHIE] He's desperately trying
to please Lord Grandfather,
no doubt.
[JOSEPH] Hmm. In any case,
Edward's bias in regard
to the test is unflattering.
[DOROTHY] Notably, his treatment
of poor, last-place Kate.
Even worse,
her living doll apparently has
sunshine on the brain.
hai no nai fukai kage bakari
Ashless shadows here and everywhere I look
I no nai kotai dooru mitai
Like dolls without a self to call their own
jibun fuzai dokonimo inai
I, myself, am absent all the same
nai janai
Utterly bereft
aimai na I iro no nai I
My nebulous, colorless self
gitai igai
This mimicry, a surprise!
hitogoto mitai
As if it's not my concern
okagesama dochira sama
"And who might you be, esteemed Shadow?"
kotae samazama
Varied were our answers
nanimono demo nai mama
If I lived without a self
nan ni mo dekinai mama
If I couldn't do a thing
ikiru no wa muda desu ka
Would my life still have meaning?
warui koto desu ka
Would that be so wrong?
koko ni inai inai
It's not here, it's gone
inai no wa jibun jibun
What's gone is me, is me
dare mo minai minai
They don't see me, see me
minai mama hakisutete sayounara
Unseen, I'll be swept away, goodbye
ureshikunai
Neither joy
kanashiku mo nai
Nor sorrow
toumei na kibun
My feelings, invisible
tarinai jibun awasu kao mo nai
I'm not enough, no face to show
nai
None
There's none
nai
None
waraenai janai
No room to laugh
Trying to find a way to pass, the five pairs face the Debut.
The examiner, Edward, orders the Living Dolls to find their masters
in the garden maze, and reach the exit together within the two
hours until the soot clock runs out. Emilyko and the other Living Dolls,
sometimes working together, search for their masters. Meanwhile,
Kate realizes that the Debut is being monitored by someone...
Trying to find a way to pass, the five pairs face the Debut.
The examiner, Edward, orders the Living Dolls to find their masters
in the garden maze, and reach the exit together within the two
hours until the soot clock runs out. Emilyko and the other Living Dolls,
sometimes working together, search for their masters. Meanwhile,
Kate realizes that the Debut is being monitored by someone...
The five Living Dolls use the map and tools they received
to hurry to their captured masters. But there are many
tricks and traps in the garden that block their path. Will
each of the five pairs find each other and safely reach
the exit, passing the Debut...?
The five Living Dolls use the map and tools they received
to hurry to their captured masters. But there are many
tricks and traps in the garden that block their path. Will
each of the five pairs find each other and safely reach
the exit, passing the Debut...?
Next Episode
An Incomplete Map
[KATE] Next episode,
"An Incomplete Map."