Please tell us
where our masters are.
The rules are fairly simple.
Obviously, you must
exit the garden
before the allotted
time expires.
But first, you must
save your masters.
What have you done to them that
they would need rescuing from?
[EDWARD]
Of course you're concerned.
It's important
you feel that way.
After all, living dolls exist
for the sake of their masters.
Why is it even necessary
for you to put us
through this whole thing?
Such questions are
trivial... immaterial!
Do remember: You must
carefully consider
what you should and shouldn't
allow into your thoughts.
Protecting your masters comes
first, for they are nobles.
In addition, no harm must
come to a living doll's face
while in the labyrinth.
And a shadow's attire
must not get dirty.
It takes approximately
two hours for the soot to go
from the bottom to top
in the sootglass.
You must bring your master to
the exit before that happens.
Take this and wait
at the entrance
I told each of you to go to.
In the Palm of His Hand
How awful. Her dress
has been sewn to the chair.
The Fragile Flower.
[RICKY] "This flower causes
a rash if touched."
Each of our shadow masters
has been restrained
in a different manner.
[RICKY gasps]
Wh-What a pleasant surprise.
[RICKY]
I don't even know her name.
[RICKY] We have all
been tasked with saving
our own masters
from confinement.
I'm sure that Rum
will come along any time now.
[RICKY grunts]
[LOU]
Let's go.
[RICKY]
How creepy.
You and Rum can be
unnervingly quiet,
but her silence is
a different kind of scary.
[LOU]
You dare to criticize her?
[gasps]
What? No!
I-I meant scary, but, only in
a reverential way, of course!
You misunderstood me!
Also...
I would appreciate it
if you could remove that sack.
[LOU]
It protects my face.
Your mask actually
gave me the idea.
Oh. Right.
Just like me.
When the chips are down,
you always make sure
you're looking out
for Number One.
Like when you saw
Mistress Kate from afar,
but didn't offer
to help her down.
Guess you're done pretending
to be friends with poor Emilico?
[LOU]
Emilico will save Mistress Kate.
Rum will save
her own shadow master.
And I'm going to rescue
my Mistress Louise.
It's simple.
[RICKY] Damn her
for being so unflappable.
But Mistress Kate, she told me
I was fine just the way I am.
And so I have no right
or reason not to believe her.
[growls]
[RICKY]
All of them are just so...
How could I not be the most
outstanding doll of the lot?
No way I'm losing
to miscreants like them!
[RICKY grunts]
[RICKY] Look at that!
A soot plume in the sky.
It's Mistress Louise.
[gasps]
[RICKY]
The soot disappeared.
Where could it have gone?
[RICKY] Hmm.
And what makes you think
that it was Mistress Louise?
All we could see was some soot.
Because I observed the other
shadow masters when we were
in the debut hall.
Mistress Kate's soot
goes straight up.
Master John's looks like sparks.
Master Patrick's emanates
in all directions.
I didn't see anything
from Rum's mistress.
But Mistress Louise's
soot curls.
[RICKY] They emit soot
in different patterns?
I had no idea.
Quite the observant one.
She noticed that. Saw it in
Master Patrick before I did.
[LOU] But I don't know
what happened to her.
If she were here,
she'd call out to me.
After all,
Mistress Louise loves me.
[RICKY] Perhaps something
is preventing her
from being able to speak.
Yes, that's it!
This test must also be designed
for the shadow masters.
But just what are
they being tested for?
That soot we just saw
may have been an accident,
but it drew us to this garden.
Indicating to us that a shadow
master has to be hidden
somewhere on the premises.
Considering where
we've looked so far,
this part should be simple.
After all, shadow masters emit
soot when they're anxious.
Well, it would seem
my Mistress isn't here.
I should go look elsewhere.
But a shadow master is here!
[LOU]
Shh! I have a plan.
Mistress Louise cannot get
enough of either my face
or my voice.
[RICKY grunts] You know, you
don't have to keep bragging
about your relationship.
My Master Patrick
also tells me that...
Quiet. Simply hearing
the sound of my voice
will put my Mistress at ease.
[RICKY gasps]
[LOUISE whimpers]
Make a rope ladder to save her.
[LOU] "Make a rope ladder
to rescue her."
Make a rope ladder to save her.
[LOUISE gasps, chuckles]
How positively horrible!
But it's over, thanks
to dependable Lou!
And how lovely you look!
[LOUISE]
Oh? Who is this?
[LOU] Ricky. He helped me
get here in time to find you.
O lovely Mistress Louise,
it is my sincerest pleasure
to be at your service.
[LOUISE]
How repulsive!
[RICKY gasps]
[LOUISE] You followed
Louise's lovely face
all this way, did you?
A living doll attracted
to a shadow's face?
The absolute cheek!
Remember your place.
[RICKY] No, Mistress,
you have it all wrong.
[LOUISE]
Or perhaps, your Master Patrick
is fond of Louise, is that it?
What a pity, but we think not.
Patrick is but a minor figure.
The answer is emphatically
in the negative!
[RICKY]
Lou...
[RICKY gasps]
[LOUISE]
Now, your work is done here.
You won't be needed further.
Ah, how Louise missed her face!
Lou, let's have
a good look at you.
How terribly shocking
it was to hear you say
you were going to leave!
You were relying on Louise's
soot to seek her out,
were you not?
Ah! Oh, we must hurry back to
the debut hall if we are to win!
[RICKY] Arrogant fools.
Their guards are down.
If I were to shove them
into one of these pits...
Hmm...
[EMILICO]
Here's the dreadful maze.
The one Master John
told us about before.
Let's go!
[gasps] I was not expecting
all of those scorches
on the other side!
[EMILICO]
That gave me goosebumps.
[gasps] I'd say this is the
perfect time to make
a you-know-what!
Sorry?
Ah!
I knew right from the beginning
that I could make one.
I chose the pushcart so
that I'd be able to collect
whatever I needed.
And the handle is just perfect
for making my own broom!
[RUM] I thought she chose
the pushcart in order to carry
her Mistress back more quickly!
Then, that little satchel
of essentials we received
from Edward gave me
another good idea.
[EMILICO] If I want to
help Mistress Kate return
to her everyday life
most efficiently...
then I must start
by dressing as I always have!
[gasps]
[EMILICO]
It's a bit off, but it'll do.
[RUM]
No matter what,
Emilico always has
Mistress Kate on her mind.
[RUM]
And yet, my Mistress and I...
Right then, are you
ready to do this?
We're going in!
Take that!
They run when hit from above!
Let's try sideways!
[SCORCHES screaming]
[RUM gasps]
[EMILICO grunts]
Got one, nice work, Rum!
[RUM]
Let's see...
We take the path
to the left here,
and at the next branch,
we turn right.
[grunts] Wow, that's
one impressive memory
you've got there!
But something is wrong...
We've gone too far.
[EMILICO] Huh?
[RUM gasps]
The path never branched off,
or if it did,
then we must've
missed it somehow!
[EMILICO] Hmm... I wonder
how this happened.
It's all wrong.
This maze is nothing
like the one on the map.
It was probably a trick.
[EMILICO]
Do you really think so?
Wah!
[RUM whimpering]
[screams]
[EMILICO]
I'll take care of the scorches!
That way, you can focus on
trying to figure out the map!
[gasps]
[RUM] Emilico is counting
on me to make this work.
But I don't know if I can!
What do you think, Rummy?
[RUMMY] There is more to what
Edward told us than mere lies.
Some sort of hint has to exist.
[RUM]
A hint?
Everything Master John said
about this maze was true.
It really is dreadful!
[RUM gasps]
[JOHN] The bridge John
crossed to get there...
Two Crossings Only
It collapsed.
[gasps]
Hold on, look up there!
[EMILICO gasps]
Ah! It's a hut mark,
like the one on the map!
Well, if that mark up there
is accurate, then...
that means our
current position must be...
I've got it now! It means
we are in the lower area
of the maze,
surrounded by massive walls.
[RUM gasps] If we're surrounded,
is there no exit?
We're stuck here?
No! See how "up" is written
inside of that hut mark?
So there has to be
a way up somewhere!
Let's go look for it!
[BOTH panting]
I think that tunnel
over there goes up.
[EMILICO]
Here we go!
[BOTH panting]
Look! We've found our way out!
[RUM]
And more scorches...
They're persistent.
With us both pushing the cart,
though, that means no broom.
Let's go.
[gasps]
Yes! All right, it's time
to stomp some soot!
Heave-ho!
[EMILICO]
Hang on!
[skittering]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH grunt]
[panting]
We did it!
Well now, look at
that over there.
[EMILICO] A hole cut out of
the hedge, like a shortcut
to where the map showed
Mistress Shirley was being held!
[RUM]
Is it... a trap?
Of course! I bet Lou cut out
this hole using her shears!
Without knowing, we've
been helping each other
all throughout the test!
Now you can climb through
and see Mistress Shirley!
[RUM sighs]
We've been working as
a team this whole time,
so it's a bit sad to part ways,
but at least now you'll get
to be with your Mistress again!
[RUM whimpers]
What's wrong?
Are you feeling poorly?
Did those scorches
back there hurt you?
Once I've made sure
Mistress Kate is safe,
I'll try to come back
and give you a hand.
[RUM]
It's not that...
[sobs]
It's Mistress Shirley...
Rum isn't her face.
[RUM sobbing]
[EMILICO]
If that's the case,
then who's your
true shadow master,
and how do we get
you back to her?
No, she's...
What I mean...
is I'm not Rum!
[gasps] Wait. What happened
to the real Rum, then?
It's me.
The thing is, Mistress Shirley
never gave me a name.
[EMILICO gasps]
[RUM] It's shameful, but we've
never had a single conversation.
It was after Rummy and I
started talking to each other.
That's when Rummy
first called me Rum.
Mistress Shirley doesn't
even pretend to care about me.
I am nothing. I have no right
to even try and save her.
Rum, I had no idea...
And to top it all off,
the only one
I ever think about is myself.
And the way you're always
thinking of Mistress Kate
makes me wonder
what's wrong with me.
Instead, the only thing
I was concerned with was
if I'd succeed at the debut.
And it wasn't until this moment
that I thought about her.
[RUM]
Mistress Shirley...
She emits next to no soot,
and her room barely needs
any cleaning.
And so... there's
nothing for me to do!
I'll do whatever I can
to make it past the debut,
but I have no idea if Mistress
Shirley feels the same way.
[sobs]
I just can't tell... at all!
[whimpers]
[EMILICO] It's tough not being
able to see our masters clearly.
But because we can't, I try
to use my imagination instead.
[gasps]
[EMILICO] It's not easy to be
a member of the Shadows family.
Their soot is only able to
express negative emotions.
And besides,
they can't see themselves.
I'd feel anxious, too.
Mistress Kate and I don't always
get along as well as we should,
but still...
We don't want to make
their lives any harder
than they already are.
Or sadder.
So I'd rather liven
things up a bit by having
as much fun as possible!
After what you said,
I can't stop thinking
about Mistress Shirley.
Imagination time!
Maybe she's like you and gets
nervous when she has to talk.
And if she doesn't
emit very much soot,
it could mean that
she's satisfied with you.
Huh?
[EMILICO] What if she just
enjoys cleaning so much,
she does most of it
before you arrive?
Or just think: she could be
trying to get you to laugh
by always making funny faces.
I hope I don't get in trouble
for saying something so silly.
[giggles]
[EMILICO chuckles]
[RUM sighs]
[RUMMY]
I just want to pass the debut.
[RUM]
I really do.
With Mistress Shirley!
Ha! That's right, and after
we've made it through,
we can officially meet
again as Mistress Kate
and Mistress Shirley's faces!
With all my heart,
I hope you can be friends
with Mistress Kate, too!
[RUM giggles]
See you in a little while!
[sighs]
[metal clanking]
[KATE gasps]
One of the chains holding
the cage... just broke?
What's going on?
[KATE]
Another?
If they were to all break...
That vent, it appears to be
drawing in the soot plume.
Are the chains designed to break
as the soot accumulates?
If it doesn't stop...
[gasps]
It's no use.
I can't stop it!
Controlling the soot
does nothing to get rid of
these negative feelings.
Emilico...
Mistress Kate!
[KATE gasps]
Emili... co?
[ALLIE]
It's nearing completion.
[JER]
This seems a bit excessive,
but the view is marvelous.
[ALLIE] The veiled dolls are
certainly out in force today.
I say, Edward.
It's not everyday one sees
a debut on this scale.
Some end with little fanfare,
before they've
even left the hall.
This has got your personality
written all over it, Ed.
I'd be hard-pressed to think
of a more enjoyable debut for
the latest candidates,
assuming they can even enjoy it.
As long as this situation
proceeds according to plan,
nothing else is important.
Provided I entertain those
on the third floor.
I should be worthy enough for
Lord Grandfather's attention.
You aren't really hoping to
ascend to the third floor?
Why, Ed? You already
have plenty of power
at your disposal
on the second floor.
[EDWARD] Upon arrival
at Lord Grandfather's
wing of the estate,
I found three different floors,
and each one had
its own ranking.
I must rise to the apex itself.
The eminent figures
on the third floor
don't even send out their faces.
I say it's time they
open up a spot for me.
It would be prudent not to
speak lightly of such things.
[EDWARD]
Have no fear, Jer.
[JER sighs] I merely wish to
avoid any unnecessary concerns.
Proceed cautiously.
I shouldn't need to remind
you that of the candidates
at our debut,
only we three remain.
Should we not be paying
more attention to
the current candidates?
Look. The details
on all five pairs.
I've already perused this.
[ALLIE] So? On what will
you base your decision?
Information on the soot and
refuse taken from their rooms,
as well as the
Star Bearers' reports.
I've already chosen
each one's roles.
This one's potential
could be coaxed to fruition.
There are outstanding
candidates, as well,
which I took into account
when balancing the game.
And this is the one
who will ultimately fail.
Such limited soot emissions,
and a meager appetite.
[EDWARD]
As for this one...? Who knows?
They seem perfectly ordinary,
yet the information is flawless.
It's almost as if they know
they're being watched.
Is something wrong, Edward?
[EDWARD]
No, at least, nothing important.
Surely, you must be looking
forward to the drama?
[EDWARD] You already know
the answer, Allie.
It's a resounding "no."
Nothing can be allowed
to disturb the plans
for my perfect world.
Of course not.
[JER] Yet again,
we simply do as we always have.
Edward will go on point, and
we'll provide you with support.
Still, since you get to be the
face interacting with all those
new kids on the big stage,
it's hard not to envy you.
If Lady Aileen and
Lord Gerald kept
the third-floor lords
entertained, it would truly be
worth envying.
Come now, Ed.
Spare me your sarcasm.
Must they send these
inane messages?
[EDWARD] Barring the path
to this plaza merely spoils
the beauty of the landscape.
[EDWARD] Those dolls I'd
first taken for dullards,
keep finding the clever
puzzles I put in their path.
And worse, keep solving them.
[EDWARD (SHADOW)]
However...
Edward has all the little
fools in the palm of his hand!
What a beautiful melody!
♪
As Living Dolls and Shadow masters begin meeting, Ram is
encouraged by Emilyko. They promise to pass the Debut and meet
again, and head towards their masters. All participants are making
surprisingly steady progress, but even though Edward must fail
someone, he plays the piano undisturbed, basking in self-satisfaction.
As Living Dolls and Shadow masters begin meeting, Ram is
encouraged by Emilyko. They promise to pass the Debut and meet
again, and head towards their masters. All participants are making
surprisingly steady progress, but even though Edward must fail
someone, he plays the piano undisturbed, basking in self-satisfaction.
Next Episode
Birdcage and Flowers
[KATE] Next episode,
"A Birdcage and Flowers."