[LORD GRANDFATHER] Faces will
lose their sense of self
in due time, becoming
but faithful servants
to their shadows.
Then, shall shadow
and face merge together
as a complete being,
united as one.
[JOSEPH] Mm. That
inevitable end, however,
calls into question the
methods of Edward's debut.
[RYAN] It's a mistake to have
a shadow be friendly
with their face.
Faces are only
meant to be taken.
Therefore, making them
rescue their masters
is ridiculously
counter-productive.
It creates an emotional bond
and encourages them
to think for themselves.
[DOROTHY] But consider... it's
important to promote loyalty,
is it not? Although,
it is quite a risk,
presenting a debut
which they could all fail.
[SOPHIE]
A fascinating experiment.
Some even show signs
of new powers blossoming.
In that respect,
Sophie is impressed with Edward.
[RYAN] Tch! You wish to
mass-produce Star Bearers?
Mark Ryan's words:
no good will come of them
ponder over matters.
[LORD GRANDFATHER] This means
there are yet many possibilities
here in Shadows House.
What an interesting debut
this is turning out to be.
[JOSEPH] Edward's methodology
is revolutionary.
It will be difficult for him
to come to a swift judgement.
[RYAN]
Bah! That Edward...
He makes one's blood boil.
He's rolled out quite
the lavish performance.
Why? Is he trying
to steal Ryan's thunder?
[DOROTHY]
No, no, come, now.
However, that was uncalled for.
[SOPHIE] The union of bodies
is the house's great secret.
It was foolish to do so
where the candidates...
might bear witness.
[AILEEN] Ed, you've sunk
too far into your own world.
[DOROTHY]
Aileen!
[AILEEN]
Yes, ma'am.
[LORD GRANDFATHER]
What becomes of these five pairs
upon the debut's conclusion
shall be a sight to see.
Of that, there is no doubt.
Birdcage and Flowers
[JOHN] Oh, how wonderful
it feels to once again
be wearing clean clothes!
Ah, the soot remover is superb!
There would be no more need
to change three times a day
with one of those on hand!
Then there's this map.
This debut is so much fun!
Well, Shaun? Do you think
we can get through the bars?
I was able to figure it out.
They're locked by this bar
sunk into the ground, here.
They should turn if we lift it.
But there's also a bar
on the other side.
It appears that both
of them have to be lifted
at the same time.
[JOHN] So, we can't
actually move it
without someone on that side?
There's nothing that we can do.
We'll just have to
take a little detour.
But we'll be able to check on
Mistress Kate on the way.
[JOHN]
No, John's not going to see her.
He promised not to
until he passed this test.
All right, we won't, then.
[JOHN] Believe it, John would
save her if she asked!
[sighs]
I won't lie, you're the last
person I wanted to see.
Same here.
Ahh. That makes sense.
Now, then, you want to be
on this side, right, Shaun?
Why don't you get down
on your knees and beg?
Maybe then I'll help you.
I'm not an idiot... if you
came from that direction,
then you must want
to get to this side.
Nah. I've already
saved Master Patrick,
so now, I'm just trying
to kill some time
with a nice little stroll.
[JOHN]
Is that Patrick's face?
[RICKY gasps]
Master John?!
It just kills you, doesn't it?
That I've figured out more of
the labyrinth than you have.
In fact, I even know
where Master Patrick is.
All of your bluster was in vain.
Considering where
you are right now,
it's obvious that you
haven't saved him yet,
and this is no little stroll.
[RICKY growls]
[JOHN] Shaun? Can John
ask you a question?
Yes?
[JOHN] Doesn't having
your master here give you
an unfair advantage?
John would like to learn
all about the relations
between dolls.
So, please, proceed
as if John weren't here.
But if you order him to help us,
Ricky will have to obey you.
[JOHN]
Hmph!
[SHAUN sighs]
He certainly is
a unique shadow master.
Well, I've still got
the advantage in my case.
We have plenty of time left,
even with a detour.
I already know
most of the paths.
However, you have
a considerable way to go
before you'll see
Master Patrick.
Your path will take you about
twice around the entire garden.
[RICKY growls]
I'll tell you what, though.
If you'll apologize
for hitting me,
then I would be happy
to lend you a hand.
[RICKY grunts]
Well done. One point to Shaun.
[RICKY]
Not so fast.
[SHAUN, JOHN]
Hmm?
From what you've said,
can I go ahead and assume
that Master Patrick is here?
I really had no idea before now.
I must thank you from
the bottom of my heart
for your loose-lipped leak.
That's one for Ricky.
[SHAUN gasps]
This is ridiculous.
I'm done wasting time here.
Master, let's go now.
[RICKY]
No, wait! Fine, I'll apologize!
[grunts]
[monotone]
Hitting you was so very wrong.
[SHAUN] Well, that was
utterly insincere,
but drawing this out will only
end up wasting more time.
Emilico would probably help him,
no questions asked.
All right, then,
let's open the gate.
[JOHN] Huh? But it's still tied
two to two, isn't it?
[SHAUN]
Hey, that's enough about that!
And wait a minute, when did
we each score another point?
Okay, we'll lift up
the bars together.
[RICKY]
Hmph.
[SHAUN gasps]
Aren't those
the shears Lou chose?
Ricky, what have
you done to her?
Nothing. Lou gave them
to me, obviously.
I swear upon Master Patrick,
that I'm not lying to you.
But why would Lou
give you her shears?
It doesn't make any sense!
You've tried to trick people
into doing your bidding
this whole time.
How am I supposed to trust you?
[RICKY]
Tsk.
[SHAUN] Wait! Come back here
and answer me!
You're not gonna believe me
no matter what I say!
And that's just the same
as insulting Master Patrick!
Hmph!
[bells clanging]
[JOHN] Hmm?
[SHAUN] Hmm?
[clanging continues]
[applause]
[VOICES]
Mistress Louise has arrived!
[LOUISE] To think we'd be
greeted so grandly at the exit!
How delightful it feels
to come in first.
[LOU grunts]
There's Barbie.
Sounds like Louise
has made it out.
And that means... Ricky was
actually telling the truth.
[RICKY growls]
[LOUISE]
Ah, how Louise missed her face!
Lou, let's have
a good look at you.
[RICKY] A living doll should
never lay their hands
on a shadow master.
I'm not some fool who'd let a
moment of passion overwhelm me
into disgracing Master Patrick.
[LOU]
Ricky?
[RICKY gasps]
Here you go.
These are Mistress
Louise's orders?
Oh, no. It has nothing
to do with her.
It's a secret.
[LOU] I just...
I wanted you to have them.
[RICKY gasps]
I've never done
anything like this before.
Feels strange. But I had fun
while I was with you.
[RICKY gasps]
I want you and
Master Patrick to succeed.
To make it past the debut.
[gasps]
[growls]
[SHAUN]
Ricky!
I owe you an apology!
I'm sorry for doubting you!
Come back!
Will Ricky abandon
this path out of pride?
Interesting.
Too bad the path you've chosen
doesn't lead to the finish line.
Alas, I'm afraid
it's all over for you.
Looks like that
half-wit was right.
I don't stand a chance
if I take this detour.
Damn it all.
[rumbling]
Huh...?
Ah!
[JOHN]
Whew. Ricky's on his way back.
Huh...?
[RICKY] Help me!
Uh!
What the...?!
[screams]
[RICKY panting]
[SHAUN, JOHN]
Boulder!
[RICKY grunts]
Lift up the bar on your side!
[SHAUN] Look, I'd like to help
you, except that means I'd be
the one who's in danger!
Hang on! I'll think
of something.
[RICKY growls] You must care
for Master Patrick.
[gasps]
He's more sensitive
than you might think.
I fear he won't handle it
very well once I'm gone.
Who knows what
will happen to him
if he doesn't pass the debut?
But, Shaun, if he does
end up surviving this...
you have to
help him, all right?!
Please! You, too, Master John!
[SHAUN grunts, gasps]
Master John!
[JOHN]
This body has a mind of its own!
No, you can't! Master John!
Master John!
[JOHN yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[JOHN]
Priceless face, Ricky!
And that's three points!
[BOTH]
Ah...!
What was that...?
[SOPHIE gasps]
How marvelous...
It's such an enormous
amount of soot!
If only one could get
a closer look!
John, come back!
Give us a little lick...
You should be careful, Sophie.
You're so excited,
your face is showing.
[AILEEN]
Her face is showing?
[GERALD]
So it seems.
[SOPHIE sighs]
[SOPHIE] Livening up the moment
is always a fine thing.
Yes, so they say,
and it's usually true.
[DOROTHY]
Sophie, you change completely
when it comes to soot.
It's frightening.
It would seem this
rather curious debut
is coming to its end.
[RYAN] Look, why do these
three keep going in circles?
Well, because John
went to the other side
and now he must get back,
but he can't actually
rejoin Shaun on
the safe side unless Ricky
trades places with him.
[RYAN chuckles] A heroic effort
wasted by a feeble fool.
[SOPHIE]
Look at Rum, though.
She appears to be advancing.
[JOSEPH] That is the tunnel
Ricky opted not to take.
[RYAN] Did Miss Sunshine
put some ideas in her head?
She's become positively valiant.
John and Shaun are heading
for the exit now.
And Ricky and Rum are
reuniting with their masters.
The living dolls are
forced to grow up fast...
Overcoming all
these difficulties.
[RYAN] Hah! He's so pleased,
he's chatting up a storm,
but the question remains,
can he open the crate?
[DOROTHY]
Who cares? It's adorable.
[SOPHIE]
Oh? He's noticed something.
[SOPHIE] The various
confines Edward designed...
All of them have
soot as their key.
Ricky has found a very
useful mold for making a key
from hardened soot.
[JOSEPH]
John was also in a crate,
but he used his
powers to destroy it.
[SOPHIE] It seems Ricky
has learned a few things
from Louise's rescue and
John's wondrous power.
[DOROTHY]
How magnificent!
[RYAN] Well, he's soundly
cleared that hurdle.
[JOSEPH] The faces gain
the trust of their masters,
who praise them
for their efforts.
Thus, their bond deepens.
[JOSEPH] Unfortunately, Shirley
has yet to emit any soot.
This may prove difficult.
[DOROTHY]
What's this?
She's channeling
Miss Sunshine's resourcefulness!
[RYAN]
She'd better be careful.
The sap will splatter all over.
[DOROTHY] This is too
nerve-wracking to watch.
Doesn't she know it
causes a burning rash?
[JOSEPH] Like Kate's cage,
the upper area comes loose
if exposed to soot.
The rash-causing flowers
were meant to fall on her.
She found a workaround.
[DOROTHY] Rum seemed
quite wishy-washy at first,
but she is
unexpectedly resolute.
[SOPHIE] It's an act
of loyalty toward Shirley.
[DOROTHY] What's this?
Is Shirley speaking...?
[SOPHIE]
An emotional reunion.
How unfortunate
we cannot hear them.
[RYAN] The worst candidates
staged a comeback.
[JOSEPH]
Patrick and Ricky took a detour,
but at this rate,
they'll likely make it in time.
[RYAN] Here comes the grand
finale to an excellent debut.
[RYAN] They'd better not
all make it together,
merrily holding hands,
because Ryan couldn't stomach
such an imbecilic ending!
Well, Gerald?! Aileen?!
[SOPHIE] Shadows House
is not so kind as to keep
the incompetent around.
[JOSEPH] The fact is,
that at every debut,
there have been
useless individuals.
[RYAN]
And if Edward cannot find them,
then he has failed in his task.
[DOROTHY]
Now, now, hold on, Ryan.
This debut isn't
over quite yet, is it?
Those two are still in play.
The most pitiful of all.
[EMILICO]
Mistress Kate!
Mistress Kate...
It really is you.
[whimpers]
How silly... I mustn't cry yet.
I'm just so glad you're safe!
I was so worried.
I couldn't wait to see you.
Ah! Forgive me, Mistress Kate!
I imagine this made you far
more anxious than even I was.
[KATE] No, though it would've
been nice to have a book.
It was so very dull.
But... you must have had
a terrible time getting here.
Yes! Lots and lots of crazy
stuff has been happening!
[KATE]
Mm. Oh, really? Do tell.
[EMILICO]
First, we were told to proceed
through the garden alone.
[KATE]
That must've been lonely.
[EMILICO] I saw lots of
strange puzzles and traps.
We would've had fun
strolling it together, I think!
[KATE]
Kate wishes she could have.
[EMILICO] I met some of
the other masters and dolls
along the way, and together,
we were able to solve
some mysteries!
[KATE] Really? John happened
to come across Kate.
He's an odd one.
[EMILICO]
I saw him, too!
Believe it or not,
he was a lot of fun.
Ah! Hey, would you
like an orange?
[KATE]
Maybe later.
Oh, what a lovely apron.
[EMILICO]
Hurray!
I specifically hoped you would
like it as I was working on it!
[KATE] Seeing you look like
you always do is reassuring.
[EMILICO] You know the wonderful
thing this test has shown me?
That all the dolls hold their
masters dear, just as I do.
[KATE]
That's right.
[EMILICO] Also, I defeated
a bunch of scorches!
[KATE]
They made you do that?!
Are you hurt?
I'm perfectly fine!
So tell me, what did you think
about while you waited for me?
Oh, just your reaction
whenever I give you that bread
you love so much.
[EMILICO, KATE giggle]
[KATE] Let's continue
this later over a cup of tea
in Kate's room, shall we?
Yes!
Kate has something she'd
like to talk to you about.
[bells clanging]
[EMILICO gasps]
Hey, do you hear that?
It's the bell again.
[KATE]
Someone must have passed.
You can just see
the exit from here.
It's not clear who, but someone
is definitely being greeted.
Now, about how Kate
ended up in this predicament.
The controls for this cage
are located on the other side
of these big thorn trees, there.
Edward said it was necessary
for the debut and would
brook no argument, so there
was no choice but to get in.
As he operated the controls,
the crane started to move,
dangling this cage
where you now see it.
The problem is the cage itself.
As soon as soot enters
the ceiling vent,
the chains by which
it's hung break.
It's only hanging
by five chains now.
Oh, no! We have
to do something!
How do I get over there?
Can you see any way?
[KATE] Yes, there is a path
right behind the cage.
However, I'm afraid
the entrance is locked.
Edward said something
about the key being available
at the sootglass plaza.
[gasps]
The keys! He must mean those!
[sighs]
[KATE]
You don't have them...?
[EMILICO whimpers]
[EDWARD]
There was but one chance.
Out of my great benevolence,
I provided one guaranteed way
of passing the challenge.
You had to choose the keys
right at the beginning.
The truth is, you were doomed
to fail the moment you exited
the sootglass
plaza without them.
[KATE]
Emilico, what are you doing?
[EMILICO] You said the controls
are on the other side
of these thorn trees, right?
[KATE] Well, yes. True,
but I didn't mean for you...
If I can cut through here,
I can save you!
So, that's what
I'm determined to do!
You just never give up.
No matter what.
Kate really
likes that about you.
[KATE gasps]
[EMILICO]
Mistress Kate!
I better hurry...
[KATE]
But...
[EMILICO panting]
[KATE]
There's no time.
[EDWARD] Yes! I knew
Emilico wouldn't give up!
How marvelous!
Go on, show those third-floor
masters how you'll struggle
in vain until the very end!
[KATE screams]
Oh, Mistress Kate!
[KATE]
Only two chains left!
[EMILICO growls]
[KATE] Emilico is trying
her hardest, but I...
[leaves rustling]
[KATE gasps]
Emilico. Someone's coming.
Oh, it's Ricky.
[KATE]
Patrick? Why now?
[EMILICO] Hold on, those are
the shears that Lou chose,
aren't they?
Kind of a long story.
[KATE]
Did he steal them from Louise?
I wouldn't be surprised if he
thought that eliminating rivals
would give him an extra edge.
I knew it. We can't trust
the other pairs.
[EMILICO]
What a relief!
[KATE gasps]
That means the last bell
or the one right before it
must have been for Lou!
And I bet she was so grateful
for your help along the way
that she gave you the shears
to thank you, didn't she?
[RICKY gasps]
Mm.
[KATE gasps]
[GROUP gasping]
[EMILICO] Mistress Kate!
Are you all right?!
[KATE]
Yes, but...
Sorry! I'm afraid
I can't talk right now.
I have something very urgent
I must take care of!
Ah!
[PATRICK] Give Emilico
the shears to use
for her task, Ricky.
[EMILICO gasps]
There is a debt to pay.
Thank you so much for this!
Now, I'll save Mistress Kate
and all will be well!
Because Shaun, and Rum,
and Ricky, and Lou...
They're all pulling
for our success!
[KATE] It certainly didn't
start out that way.
They've changed because of you.
I was a total fool.
From the very start, I made
enemies here, not friends.
[KATE] Emilico! It will take
too long to cut it all down.
Just cut enough
for you to get through.
And please, be careful
you don't get hurt!
Yes, ma'am!
[EMILICO]
Mistress Kate! I made it!
I've reached
the crane's controls!
[KATE] Well done!
Do you know how to use it?
[EMILICO gasps] Uh-oh, it looks
like I need a key here, too!
That's not good...
[KATE]
Oh no! The soot is about to...!
[KATE] It's no use.
The soot won't stop coming.
At any moment, I'll...
[KATE]
I'm scared... This is awful...
I'm so scared!
Don't worry, I'm not giving up!
[KATE gasps]
[EMILICO yells] I'm determined
to save you, no matter what!
[KATE]
Emilico!
[gasps]
Ah!
[KATE groaning]
[EMILICO]
I'm coming!
[yells]
Mistress Kate!
[KATE gasps]
Give me your hand! Let's go!
[KATE]
Ah.
[EMILICO] You know,
I remember Mia once told me
that she was born brilliant,
but I guess...
in my case, it seems I was
born with a sturdy body instead!
hai no nai fukai kage bakari
Ashless shadows here and everywhere I look
I no nai kotai dooru mitai
Like dolls without a self to call their own
jibun fuzai dokonimo inai
I, myself, am absent all the same
nai janai
Utterly bereft
aimai na I iro no nai I
My nebulous, colorless self
gitai igai
This mimicry, a surprise!
hitogoto mitai
As if it's not my concern
okagesama dochira sama
"And who might you be, esteemed Shadow?"
kotae samazama
Varied were our answers
nanimono demo nai mama
If I lived without a self
nan ni mo dekinai mama
If I couldn't do a thing
ikiru no wa muda desu ka
Would my life still have meaning?
warui koto desu ka
Would that be so wrong?
koko ni inai inai
It's not here, it's gone
inai no wa jibun jibun
What's gone is me, is me
dare mo minai minai
They don't see me, see me
minai mama hakisutete sayounara
Unseen, I'll be swept away, goodbye
ureshikunai
Neither joy
kanashiku mo nai
Nor sorrow
toumei na kibun
My feelings, invisible
tarinai jibun awasu kao mo nai
I'm not enough, no face to show
nai
None
There's none
nai
None
waraenai janai
No room to laugh
[SOPHIE]
How very thrilling!
[JOSEPH] It is getting
quite interesting, to be sure.
[RYAN]
"Interesting"?!
All it's managed to do is make
them fret over trivial matters!
Ryan was very much
looking forward to
their spectacular deaths!
[DOROTHY]
Nevertheless...
Is this not
the end of the debut?
And their end, as well?
[LORD GRANDFATHER chuckles]
As the participants' situations change, the Debut nears its conclusion.
Emilyko arrives to find Kate trapped in a birdcage.
The cage is held by chains which break in response to soot.
Below await trees full of thorns. Will Emilyko be able to save Kate...?
As the participants' situations change, the Debut nears its conclusion.
Emilyko arrives to find Kate trapped in a birdcage.
The cage is held by chains which break in response to soot.
Below await trees full of thorns. Will Emilyko be able to save Kate...?
Using her quick wit and natural toughness, Emilyko manages to save Kate.
But they do not have time to celebrate their reunion, as the soot glass shows
the very little time remaining. Will the two of them be able to reach the
exit and pass the Debut...? And what will the
Shadow Family's goal turn out to be...?
Using her quick wit and natural toughness, Emilyko manages to save Kate.
But they do not have time to celebrate their reunion, as the soot glass shows
the very little time remaining. Will the two of them be able to reach the
exit and pass the Debut...? And what will the
Shadow Family's goal turn out to be...?
Next Episode
The Final Pair
[KATE] Next episode,
"The Final Pair."