[LIVING DOLLS]
Let us ever remember.
The Shadows are
an exceptional noble family.
And to serve them
is the pride and joy
of every living
doll's existence.
[GIRL DOLL gasps]
[yelps]
[GIRL DOLL]
Uh...
Nyugh!
[stomach growls]
[GIRL DOLL]
Uh... Eh.
Hmm!
[GIRL DOLL grunting]
[grunting]
[thunk]
[GIRL DOLL yells]
[warbling]
[GIRL DOLL sighs]
[panting]
[sighs]
[GIRL DOLL]
Uh.
[yelps]
[GIRL DOLL gasps]
[GIRL DOLL] Ah. A very
good morning to you,
dear Mistress Kate.
I am the living doll who
will be in your service
beginning today.
[KATE]
Your name?
Ma'am?
[KATE]
What's your name?
You must be given one.
[GIRL]
Please!
[KATE]
Katie, Kathy, Kat...
No, those won't do.
[GIRL DOLL]
Uh...
[KATE]
Maybe later.
Yes!
The Shadow and Her Doll
[gasps]
[GIRL DOLL]
Hmm...
[KATE]
It's quite rude to stare.
[GIRL DOLL yelps]
Forgive me!
[whimpers]
[yells, grunts]
[KATE]
Kate prefers...
Go on, Mistress Kate.
Kate prefers not to
look people in the eye.
[GIRL DOLL]
If you looked at their forehead,
wouldn't it seem like you
were looking in their eyes?
[KATE]
Like this?
Well, it's not
like you can tell.
It does seem like
you're looking in my eyes!
[KATE]
You're just saying that.
[KATE] After all, no one
can see a shadow's face.
What is...?
[KATE]
The soot?
It emanates as a result of anger
or other negative emotions.
So, right now,
are you feeling negative?
[KATE]
Well... anxious, perhaps.
Anxious...
[GIRL DOLL gasps]
[KATE] Soot collects
in nooks and crannies.
I had no idea.
[GIRL DOLL]
Hmm?
[KATE] You're staring
again... please stop.
That makes Kate more anxious
than anything else.
[GIRL DOLL]
Forgive me.
[KATE sighs]
Anxious... Huh.
I feel anxious,
too, Mistress Kate.
What does this say?
I don't know.
How will I ever be of service
to Mistress Kate like this?
[GIRL DOLL humming]
[humming continues]
[yelps]
[glass shattering]
[KATE gasps]
[GIRL DOLL]
Forgive me, Mistress Kate!
[KATE] What's done is done.
Just clean it up.
[GIRL DOLL]
Yes, ma'am!
I'm sorry.
[KATE] Kate is going
to take a bath now.
Right!
I'll have this mess cleaned up
before you're done, Mistress!
[GIRL DOLL] My body doesn't
seem to be working right.
Can I fix it, maybe
by applying oil somewhere?
[GIRL DOLL grunts, yells]
[glass shattering]
[gasps] If I break,
will I be thrown out, too?
No, no! I'm perfectly fine!
I am as fit as a fiddle!
[giggles]
Ah!
[thud, crashing]
[KATE sighs]
[whines]
Oh, no, I've done it again!
It appears that dolls
can feel pain, as well.
[KATE] Clothes are not to be
used for cleaning up spills.
You're absolutely right.
But I needed a large
cloth for this job,
and I really don't mind
being dressed like this.
[KATE] Listen. The Shadows
family's living dolls
are more than mere servants.
They were created to mimic
human beings precisely.
Without faces, it's hard
to tell the members
of the Shadows family apart.
Living dolls such as yourself
also serve as our faces.
As such, we cannot have you
neglecting your appearance.
Sorry. I didn't mean to bring
shame upon your family.
[KATE] There is
so much you don't know,
but you will learn
gradually, over time.
[GIRL DOLL] Um...
[KATE] Yes?
I'm a doll that was created
by someone, aren't I?
[KATE gasps]
That's correct.
Why are we dolls
created to look human?
[KATE] Perhaps because it allows
you to move about, to work,
and serve as our faces.
And Mistress Kate,
are you human?
[KATE]
You ask too many questions.
Forgive me...
[GIRL DOLL goans, whines]
[KATE]
What is it? Are you all right?
I think... this might
be it for me.
I am broken, beyond repair.
I can't seem to move my body.
I can no longer
fulfill my duties.
I wish I could've had more time
with you, Mistress Kate...
[KATE] This will not do!
Without you, Kate cannot...
[stomach growling]
[KATE]
Huh?
Now my body is making
the sounds of death.
[KATE]
Have you eaten?
I'm only a doll.
I don't need to eat.
[KATE] Food supplies the energy
your body needs to function.
It should be delivered to your
room each and every day!
[GIRL DOLL]
Forgive me... It's my first day.
I just ate a tiny bit.
[KATE]
Well, you must eat more!
[GIRL DOLL]
I thought the rest was yours,
so I left it on the bureau.
In my room.
[KATE] Wait right here.
Kate will bring you something.
Mistress Kate...
[sighs]
Ahh! You mean it?
I can really have this?
[KATE] Of course.
[GIRL DOLL] This is the
good bread that you eat!
It isn't at all like the bread
that's brought to my room.
It's white, and soft,
and tasty-looking!
How lucky I am!
No! I won't eat it!
No matter how hungry
I get I don't want to become
such a greedy doll that I'd
dare eat my mistress's bread!
Please take it away at once!
[gasps]
[KATE] You are Kate's face,
are you not?
Uh. I am.
[KATE] Indeed. Kate would
like to see how she looks
while eating
something delicious.
Oh, you mean that's
part of my job, too?
In that case, no holding back!
Thank you!
[KATE] What is it? Does such
food not suit a living doll?
[GIRL DOLL]
So yummy!
[KATE gasps]
Tasty! I love it!
It must be the most delicious
bread in the whole world!
[KATE giggles]
Huh? Mistress Kate, why do you
seem so merry all of a sudden?
[KATE] It's just funny to see
someone so delighted over bread.
[giggles]
It's not just any bread!
Mm! It's the yummiest
bread ever made!
[laughs]
[KATE]
Don't roll around while you eat!
Kate is going to bed now.
Thank you for
your hard work today.
[GIRL DOLL]
You're welcome, but I'm afraid
I was nothing but trouble.
I'm so very happy, and the bread
you brought me was delicious.
Thank you!
[KATE]
You're welcome.
How do you feel now?
I feel great!
I am full of energy!
[KATE]
I appreciate your positivity.
Did you forget already?
Please don't stare.
[GIRL DOLL]
Forgive me.
Knowing I won't see you till
tomorrow made me feel lonely.
[KATE gasps]
You're a strange one.
[GIRL DOLL]
Good night.
[KATE groans]
[GIRL DOLL giggles]
[GIRL DOLL]
Hmm?
Hmm...
[KATE sighs]
Oh, wow, you made a sootman!
[KATE]
How long have you been there?!
[GIRL DOLL]
From the very start!
It's a masterpiece.
[KATE]
I was just passing the time.
What else could I do?
You may return to
your room if you'd like.
No! I am quite enjoying
watching you, Mistress Kate!
It makes Kate uncomfortable
to be blatantly stared at
in this way.
[GIRL DOLL giggles]
[KATE] Well, would you care
to play a game of cards?
[GIRL DOLL]
Would I ever!
Hmm...
Pardon, but how does
one read this card here?
I can't read this one
or this one, either.
[KATE gasps]
[laughing]
You taught me so much today,
and I'm ever so happy!
Now I want to study even more
so I may better serve you.
[KATE]
I'm glad.
Why don't we make a deal then:
if you will get up to clean
an hour earlier tomorrow,
then Kate will continue
with today's lesson.
[gasps]
Hurray! That's wonderful!
[GIRL DOLL]
Ah. Mistress Kate taught me
to read this letter today.
This one, too!
So that's how you write this.
Reading is quite
difficult, isn't it?
But I'm sure I'll be able
to read better tomorrow.
I can't wait!
[GIRL DOLL groans, gasps]
I slept too long!
[yells]
[whines]
[panting]
Good morning, Mistress...
[gasps]
[KATE]
Good morning.
[GIRL DOLL gasps, whimpers]
[KATE]
You're quite late.
Kate's going to take a bath.
Please clean up this mess.
Yes, ma'am!
I will do my very best!
[door clicks]
[KATE]
You've made excellent progress.
[gasps] Mistress Kate!
I could see your face!
[KATE gasps]
[GIRL DOLL]
Please stay like that a moment.
Perhaps your profile
will tell me how you feel.
Please smile for me?
Like this?
Huh... Could you perhaps try
a big, loud laugh instead?
[KATE] Kate's never done
anything like that before.
Like this.
[laughs]
[KATE] Amazing. Such laughter
with no cause whatsoever.
But what you said is right
about profiles.
They're important.
Yes, ma'am!
[GIRL DOLL]
I've finished all my cleaning.
[KATE]
Well done.
You've gotten quite dirty.
Go wash up and change.
Then we'll have tea.
Tea time, together with you?
I'll prepare at once!
There, that's better!
The tea is almost
ready, Mistress.
[KATE]
My goodness.
You only washed what you saw
in the mirror, didn't you?
Pardon?! You're right...
Please forgive me!
[KATE]
Don't worry... come here.
Let's wipe you off.
There's something that I've
been wanting to ask you about.
Do all the members of
the Shadows family
have a living doll like me?
[KATE]
Though the timing differs,
we all get a living doll
as recognition
of our coming of age.
I suppose that makes sense.
[KATE]
What is it?
[GIRL DOLL]
I was wondering...
Am I defective?
[KATE gasps]
[GIRL DOLL] Mistress Kate,
you're so prim and proper...
So utterly unlike me.
Tell me: Will I
ever be beautiful?
[KATE sighs]
[KATE]
You are beautiful already,
but I can make
you more ladylike.
You see, Kate is highly
skilled at makeovers.
Come, sit down.
Oh, no! Please, forgive me!
Forget I ever said that.
There's no need to make
such a fuss over me.
I'll be all right, thank you.
[KATE] Kate wants
to play with her doll.
Sit.
[GIRL DOLL]
It's so sparkly! I'd love one.
[KATE]
It's a makeup box.
If you learn to use it,
you can make yourself prettier.
[gasps]
What's this?
[KATE] Powder for
improving your complexion.
But you don't need
any of that yet.
Mistress Kate, I just had
the most wonderful idea!
[KATE]
Mm?
If you put some of
this powder on you,
perhaps we'll be able
to see your face.
[KATE]
No! Don't!
[gasps]
[KATE]
Forgive me for raising my voice,
but Kate does not
require such things.
I'm so sorry!
I should not have done that.
After all, I serve as
your face now, don't I?
[KATE]
It's more than that,
you're Kate's
cherished identity.
It seems like a lot
to be someone's identity.
I wonder if I'm
doing my job well.
If not, I shall
just have try harder!
[KATE]
You must be still.
Forgive me!
[KATE] Perhaps we should
play dress-up, too.
Kate's wardrobe is in that room.
Go pick something out.
Yes, ma'am!
[GIRL DOLL]
How do I look?
[KATE] Huh? Actually, it is
strictly prohibited to dress up
a living doll in
a shadow's clothes.
Ah! What?!
I'll go change at once!
[KATE]
Now I understand why.
Dolls look like perfect
models of human beings.
[GIRL DOLL]
Ah...
That's not true in the least!
[KATE gasps]
[GIRL DOLL] I don't even
notice when I get dirty,
and my behavior
is entirely uncouth.
If I wear lovely clothes, I'll
end up falling and ruining them.
The credit belongs
to Mistress Kate.
You made me look like this!
I am nothing more
than a mirror of you.
This is your face
smiling back at you!
[KATE]
Don't be presumptuous.
You don't control
Kate's emotions.
Ahh! Forgive me!
I got carried away!
That wasn't my intent.
I just thought
I felt you smiling.
[KATE sighs]
[GIRL DOLL] Oh!
And you're not emitting soot.
Is it true that you no longer
feel anxious around me?
[KATE]
Perhaps you're right.
[GIRL DOLL giggles]
[KATE]
Heh.
[GIRL DOLL]
You just laughed!
[KATE gasps]
I saw it.
It was as plain as day.
[KATE]
I've just realized.
[GIRL DOLL]
Ma'am?
[KATE] You are still in need
of a name of your own.
But it's so hard to decide.
One idea is "Emily."
That's what the heroine
of this book is called.
Emily? That's lovely!
[KATE] She's upbeat
and cheerful just like you.
[GIRL DOLL]
I'd love that name!
[KATE] But, on the other hand,
you are rather strange
and quite entertaining to watch.
You think I'm entertaining?
[chuckles]
[KATE]
How about Emily with a twist?
Perhaps "Emilico"?
Emilico.
[KATE]
Do you approve?
Yes! It's such a wonderful name!
Emilico. Starting today,
I'm Emilico. Hurray!
You're unique in your own way.
So make us proud.
I promise.
I'll do my best to be of service
to you, Mistress Kate!
Thank you so very much!
[KATE giggles]
[KATE]
Emilico.
Ma'am?
[KATE] Isn't that spot...
on the outside of the window?
The outside?
Ma'am. I do wonder.
Are other members of the Shadows
family out there, too?
[gasps, giggles]
hai no nai fukai kage bakari
Ashless shadows here and everywhere I look
I no nai kotai dooru mitai
Like dolls without a self to call their own
jibun fuzai dokonimo inai
I, myself, am absent all the same
nai janai
Utterly bereft
aimai na I iro no nai I
My nebulous, colorless self
gitai igai
This mimicry, a surprise!
hitogoto mitai
As if it's not my concern
okagesama dochira sama
"And who might you be, esteemed Shadow?"
kotae samazama
Varied were our answers
nanimono demo nai mama
If I lived without a self
nan ni mo dekinai mama
If I couldn't do a thing
ikiru no wa muda desu ka
Would my life still have meaning?
warui koto desu ka
Would that be so wrong?
koko ni inai inai
It's not here, it's gone
inai no wa jibun jibun
What's gone is me, is me
dare mo minai minai
They don't see me, see me
minai mama hakisutete sayounara
Unseen, I'll be swept away, goodbye
ureshikunai
Neither joy
kanashiku mo nai
Nor sorrow
toumei na kibun
My feelings, invisible
tarinai jibun awasu kao mo nai
I'm not enough, no face to show
nai
None
There's none
nai
None
waraenai janai
No room to laugh
Shadows House —
Within live many Shadows and their
servants, the Living Dolls. To Kate,
a girl of the Shadow Family, came
a lone Living Doll. Though awkward
at first, as they spent time together,
the distance between them shrank.
Kate named the Living Doll Emilyko.
Shadows House —
Within live many Shadows and their
servants, the Living Dolls. To Kate,
a girl of the Shadow Family, came
a lone Living Doll. Though awkward
at first, as they spent time together,
the distance between them shrank.
Kate named the Living Doll Emilyko.
Having gotten used to serving Kate,
Emilyko joined the other Living Dolls in
cleaning the mansion. She was assigned
to Rosemary's group, and diligently cleaned
together with Mia and Lou. Additionally, she
encountered the Shadow whom Mia serves,
but she was called "defective" because she
talked before her mistress, Kate.
Having gotten used to serving Kate,
Emilyko joined the other Living Dolls in
cleaning the mansion. She was assigned
to Rosemary's group, and diligently cleaned
together with Mia and Lou. Additionally, she
encountered the Shadow whom Mia serves,
but she was called "defective" because she
talked before her mistress, Kate.
Next Episode
Outside the Room
[KATE] Next time:
"Outside the Room."