The Final Pair
[EMILICO]
I'm coming!
[yells]
[KATE gasps]
Let's go!
[EMILICO] In my case,
it seems that I was born
with a sturdy body instead!
[KATE grunts]
[KATE] So, she cleared a large
area of thorn trees to give us
somewhere to land,
then she placed her pushcart
full of flowers and leaves
underneath it as a cushion.
Is it possible she
planned this from the start
in case she couldn't
operate the crane?
Truly... is there anything
this doll doesn't think of?
[KATE gasps]
Emilico, you're bleeding!
[EMILICO]
Ah.
Oh! I must have
scratched my face somehow!
Mistress Kate,
I hope you can forgive me!
[KATE]
There's a river nearby.
Let's clean it
and get you patched up.
[KATE] It's just a little
cut on your head.
It's not very deep.
Well, I guess it's true.
I am a sturdy doll!
But wait... I haven't even asked
how you're doing, Mistress Kate!
[KATE]
Kate is just fine.
Oh, I'm so glad!
Now, we're both safe and sound,
and we can still pass the test!
[KATE gasps]
Hmm...
[RYAN]
Only ten minutes remaining.
[RYAN] They still have
a long road ahead.
[bells clanging]
[KATE]
The bleeding has stopped.
Great, then let's go!
Huh?
Shouldn't we leave?
Oh, no...
Please don't tell me
it's too late...
It just can't be...
[KATE] You've been true to who
you are every step of the way.
Patrick's behavior
made that very apparent.
That's all Kate
needs to be content.
[EDWARD]
It's over!
Not everything may
have gone as planned,
but in the end,
I have succeeded.
[EDWARD]
What a moment.
This debut marks
a major step for me.
I had that one incident
in the hall,
and the living dolls proved
themselves to be tougher
than I thought.
[EDWARD] But I did foresee
the blossoming of John's power.
Of course, Ricky was nearly
flattened in the process,
but that, too, ended well.
[BARBARA]
A bit hasty, perhaps?
[EDWARD]
Hmm?
After all, the sootglass
has not yet run out.
[growls] It would take me
over ten minutes to get here
from that point,
and I know the way!
It is physically impossible
for them to make it no matter
how fast they run!
The writing's on the wall.
You kids need but do as I say,
beginning with keeping
your mouths shut!
Is that absolutely clear?!
[BARBARA]
Fine, just as you please.
[EDWARD growls]
[EDWARD]
Hmph!
[chuckles]
[thunking]
[EDWARD gasps]
What's that sound?
[CROW caws]
[EDWARD gasps]
"Check the upper level"?
What's Allie talking about?
[EDWARD]
It's going as planned.
It's going as planned!
Now, come what may, it must
all fall perfectly into place.
I have the whole
ending planned out!
[EDWARD grunts]
As for this one? Who can say?
They seem perfectly ordinary,
yet the information's flawless.
It's almost as if they know
they're being watched.
[EDWARD]
Don't tell me...
[gasps] What could
I have possibly overlooked?
[gasps]
[EMILICO]
Ah!
Ahh...!
Ahh!
[laughs]
Swinging by the river
was a good idea!
[EMILICO] I wonder where
this water comes from,
and where it goes from here.
[KATE] Well, we're on a hill,
so perhaps it connects
to a waterway that
supplies the house.
That would make sense.
Can you believe it?!
It's just like you thought!
[KATE] Yes, but converting
the pushcart into a boat
was the real stroke of genius!
Well done, Emilico.
Very impressive!
[KATE] It's true, you really
never give up, do you?
[giggles] No, but even so,
this wouldn't have worked
without you, Mistress Kate!
[KATE]
Careful, sharp turn ahead.
Ah!
[EDWARD]
Kate! Did she just...?
She can control soot! Why has
she not done so till now?
Did her power just awaken?
No! She was always capable.
She was just hiding it.
Damn it! How did I miss that?!
[gasps]
Her clothes!
[EMILICO] Look, your clothes
didn't even get dirty.
I could tell how anxious you
were feeling because you were
emitting lots of soot.
Despite all that stress,
you controlled it so that
you wouldn't get dirty.
Don't you understand,
Mistress Kate?
You never gave up, so there was
no way that I could, either!
You notice everything. You're
always watching, aren't you?
[EMILICO gasps]
Wah!
This is dangerous!
I think we should get off!
[KATE]
No, stay the course!
Wah!
[KATE] Emilico,
I wonder if you know why
I chose to name you that.
It's true that traditionally,
living dolls tend to be
given names that closely
resemble their master's.
Shadows are typically
indifferent to the name
bestowed upon their living doll.
[EMILICO whimpers]
Ah!
[KATE] But I wanted you to be
your own, unique individual,
separate from Kate.
So I gave you a unique name.
[KATE] Emilico, there's
so much I wish to tell you
once the debut is over.
I want you to know
all my secrets.
[EMILICO]
Ah...!
[KATE]
It's time to jump out!
[EMILICO screams]
[EMILICO laughs]
[VOICES]
Mistress Kate has arrived!
[bells clanging]
[KATE groans]
[EMILICO grunts]
[KATE] Apologies.
Kate's not very strong.
I felt so happy being
cradled tight in your arms
that it was worth a fall!
[SUSANNA]
This way, please.
The others who passed have
already filed into the hall.
You two were the last to arrive.
[EDWARD] If she already knew
she could control the soot
before the debut test,
why did she hide it?
What are you up to, Kate?
[applause]
[EDWARD]
Hmm? Ah!
Why are they all clapping?
Oh! Did it finally happen, then?
[SHIRLEY] Rum.
[gasps] Ah!
[SHIRLEY]
Rum.
Mistress Shirley!
How wonderful it is
to hear you say my name!
Um... Forgive me, though,
for going ahead
and choosing one for myself.
The name Rum meets
with your approval, then?
I'm so glad...
[RUM] I thought we would
make it to the exit before
the sootglass ran out.
But then, Mistress Shirley
started slowing down.
[RUM] Though we had
no hope of making it in time,
I continued holding her hand
and guiding her back.
[RUM] The sound of her
sweet voice saying my name
remained ever-present
in my mind.
Happiness was right
before me the whole time.
If only I had opened
my heart sooner,
I would have been able
to kiss her good night,
just like I always
wished I could.
[RUM sobs]
[gasps, whimpers]
[EMILICO] Ah! Now I've finally
become your face, Mistress Kate!
[BARBARA] When living
dolls wear a portrait,
they must refrain from
speaking and express
only their master's emotions.
Kate, you are free to mingle
with the other shadows,
of course. However, you must
strictly refrain from
discussing anything with them
regarding your soot powers.
That is between the Star
Bearers and those in whom
such power has awakened.
[KATE]
Understood.
[BARBARA]
Any questions?
I'm set. One need
but obey the rules.
[BARBARA]
Hmph! She's infuriating!
Let's go.
[PARTY ATTENDEES murmuring]
[applause]
[VOICE 10A]
Congratulations to Kate,
the final candidate to pass.
[murmuring]
[KATE] It appears everyone
from the children's wing
has gathered for this.
[SUSANNA]
Would you care for a cup?
[KATE]
Thank you.
What is it? It's so dark.
[SUSANNA] It's a drink served
only to shadows with faces,
in other words,
those who are deemed adults.
[KATE, EMILICO]
Bitter!
[SUSANNA laughs] Believe it or
not, once you get used to it,
you won't be able to get enough.
Drink up, and your
worries shall vanish.
[KATE] It's probably
a drink called "coffee."
It was mentioned in a book.
But Kate doesn't care for it.
She prefers tea.
But it seems like such a waste!
[KATE] You didn't seem
to care for it, either.
[groans]
[KATE giggles]
[MARYROSE]
Kate, congratulations!
I am Maryrose!
As you may know, our faces
are already well acquainted.
[EMILICO]
It's Rosemary's shadow master!
[MARYROSE]
O most beauteous Kate,
our faces are on the same team,
so it follows that you
and Maryrose shall
become quite close.
Should you have questions,
I hope that you will allow
Maryrose to guide you!
Now please be
at your ease, my lady.
[EMILICO]
She's a lady, too, right?
It's just...
she seems so gallant.
[SARAH] Maryrose!
Don't spoil the children.
[KATE]
Sarah...
[SARAH]
Well, it appears congratulations
are in order, Kate. Sarah
honestly considered you
a failure, but it seems even
the lowest-ranked shadow
managed to pass.
One gets shivers up the spine
with each visit here.
It's not every day
a shadow gets to enter
Lord Grandfather's wing.
But there will come
a day when Sarah shall be
summoned here, directly.
[MARYROSE] Of course,
this is but the first level.
It may seem like a lot after
entering from the garden,
but compared to the floors
above, this is nothing.
[SARAH] As the lowest ranked,
you're going to have to
work hard to move up.
You should try
to emulate Louise.
She would be
an excellent example.
[KATE]
Louise is at the top.
[BARBARA] Introducing: the four
pairs that have grown up today.
Please give a hand to the newest
members of the children's wing.
[applause]
[VOICE 10B] Congratulations!
Well done!
[KATE]
Four pairs?
Oh...
Emilico... you must be sad...
[BARBARA] Four of five pairs
passed this time,
a most impressive feat, indeed.
As for the single
incompetent pair that failed...
[BARBARA]
They're done!
[laughter]
[LOUISE] Oh, what a joy
to bask in this glory!
Louise is so beautiful, anyone
would love to be just like her!
[PATRICK] How can they be
so delighted in the failure
of their own kind?
And what happens
to the shadows who fail?
How should Patrick
even feel right now...?
Tell me that, Ricky...
[grunts]
No, one must learn on one's own.
Be confident, Patrick!
[JOHN] So it was Rum!
But how is she being discarded?
She was doing well!
No! One mustn't question
Shadow House's rules.
Right, Shaun?
[gasps]
[SUSANNA]
Let us adjourn to the garden!
It is time to be
received in audience.
[JOHN] Kate...
[KATE] Mm?
[BARBARA] Now, for an encounter
you shall never forget.
Presenting the noblest
of personages.
[hushed gasping]
[gasping, murmuring]
[VOICE 10C]
Lord Grandfather waved to me!
[VOICE 10D]
Such a glorious sight!
[KATE] So he's the root
of all this evil.
[EMILICO]
Ah...!
[KATE gasps]
[EMILICO giggling]
[LIVING DOLLS chuckling]
[KATE]
That dark drink they gave us!
Don't tell me...
[EDWARD]
Forgive my intrusion.
[LORD GRANDFATHER]
Now, let us see your faces.
It is an honor,
Lord Grandfather.
And as for the results...
Louise passes for facial
compatibility and soot volume.
Now John. Soot volume
above and beyond,
but personality
doesn't suit his face.
Whereas, Patrick, while
quite compatible with his face,
lacks soot volume.
And Shirley,
as you saw, my lord,
never acquired a personality.
A flaw which proved fatal.
I foresaw these outcomes based
on their pre-debut information.
The living doll Rum is horribly
inadequate as a face.
It's believed that
she never even gave
her master a kiss good night.
[DOROTHY] Edward, let us test
your knowledge, shall we?
[DOROTHY] What is a shadow,
and what is its purpose?
[EDWARD] A shadow is a form
of morph, a parasitic fairy
skilled in mimicry
and imitation.
All of us here took
this form at one time.
[EDWARD] It was Lord Grandfather
who devised the process
by which morphs
acquire personalities
and become shadows.
During stage one,
morphs are shown living dolls
so that they may recognize
and mimic the human form.
Then, in stage two,
a personality is acquired
through interaction
with said doll.
Soot powers awaken
in stage three
and unification takes place.
The shadow gains a face by
taking over the doll's body,
creating a perfect being with
powers transcending humankind.
But, if a personality is
not acquired in stage two,
we must infer the morph's
life force was too weak
to begin with.
[RYAN] Shirley certainly
fit that theory.
No wonder she
withered on the vine.
But to perish
like soot in the wind,
that was definitely a first.
It was hilarious, though
one can't help but wonder...
Edward! Tell us, did you
foresee that part happening?
No... At least,
not like that, anyway.
I wished to entertain you all.
And... I... I avoided
discarding her.
I figured the debut
could do that.
A slight error on my part led
to Shirley finally bonding
with her doll during the debut,
and though she was
already doomed to die,
her personality
began to develop.
So, you see, that's why these
unforeseen events have occurred,
or so I believe.
Perhaps I went too far in
staging a shadow's death
as some sort of show.
[DOROTHY] It is only natural
that the failures be culled.
[JOSEPH] We have need of none
but those who will prove useful
to the Lord Grandfather.
Though the manner in which
the debut was held is a concern,
as it did lead the faces to
fret over trivial matters.
[RYAN] Faces with ideas
of their own may cast doubt
upon Shadows House
if care isn't taken.
Of course, with that lot,
we can just have them drink
Grandfather's soot coffee
to alter their thinking.
It takes their
memory so swiftly.
The loyalty to Grandfather that
replaces it is breathtaking.
But what of the small percentage
of shadows who may be influenced
by the doubts of their faces?
Grandfather's soot has
no effect on shadows, after all
Indeed, the greatest risk lies
in a shadow being influenced
by their own doll's defiance.
But as long as we keep using
the coffee to make faces loyal
to Lord Grandfather,
that will, in turn,
influence their shadows, so you
really needn't be concerned.
Shirley's living doll, Rum,
was given the coffee
in order to reset her memory.
She'll soon be repurposed
as a veiled doll.
I've kept a close eye
on the malcontents,
so they don't take
root in the children's wi...
[RYAN]
You think Ryan would ever worry
about such a thing as that?!
No one would dare
defy us, you fool!
[EDWARD coughs]
Please, forgive me...
I'll take more care from now on.
[DOROTHY]
Enough about that.
Now then, Kate,
the lowest ranked of all,
I found quite amusing.
And her power has awakened...
A laudable achievement.
[EDWARD grunts]
Hmm...
[LORD GRANDFATHER]
Edward...
By utilizing this debut as
a proving ground for
the Shadows family's
potential, you hastened
a shadow's awakening,
and quite a bit more.
From this day forth,
we place the children's wing
in your care.
[LORD GRANDFATHER]
Let us see how you do.
[EDWARD]
Hmm...
[RYAN]
But don't you forget!
As judge,
you failed but one pair,
and they were already goners!
Such meager results will never
get you up to the third floor.
Understood. From now on,
I shall redouble my efforts.
It's a shame we won't rise
to the third floor just yet.
[EDWARD] Bottom line, the debut
was not to their satisfaction.
We must be of greater service to
Lord Grandfather in the future.
[EDWARD]
Ryan...
That arrogant
buffoon had the nerve
to interrupt Lord Grandfather.
Why does he even bother
to keep such frivolous fools
by his side?
I should be the one
who is serving.
Not those ne'er-do-wells.
Once I expose them, Lord
Grandfather will see the truth.
That bevy of
third-floor wastrels are
out to destroy him,
and he deserves to know!
And that means,
I must catch her in the act.
That malcontent...
Kate!
[EMILICO] I think I've become
quite efficient at cleaning,
at long last. All that's left
to do now is clean the bathroom.
[KATE] Emilico, not to intrude,
but you were close to Rum.
Aren't you shocked
by what happened?
I am. That was unfortunate.
But of course, living dolls
who are no longer of service
to Shadows House
must be discarded!
That's just the way it works!
[KATE gasps]
hai no nai fukai kage bakari
Ashless shadows here and everywhere I look
I no nai kotai dooru mitai
Like dolls without a self to call their own
jibun fuzai dokonimo inai
I, myself, am absent all the same
nai janai
Utterly bereft
aimai na I iro no nai I
My nebulous, colorless self
gitai igai
This mimicry, a surprise!
hitogoto mitai
As if it's not my concern
okagesama dochira sama
"And who might you be, esteemed Shadow?"
kotae samazama
Varied were our answers
nanimono demo nai mama
If I lived without a self
nan ni mo dekinai mama
If I couldn't do a thing
ikiru no wa muda desu ka
Would my life still have meaning?
warui koto desu ka
Would that be so wrong?
koko ni inai inai
It's not here, it's gone
inai no wa jibun jibun
What's gone is me, is me
dare mo minai minai
They don't see me, see me
minai mama hakisutete sayounara
Unseen, I'll be swept away, goodbye
ureshikunai
Neither joy
kanashiku mo nai
Nor sorrow
toumei na kibun
My feelings, invisible
tarinai jibun awasu kao mo nai
I'm not enough, no face to show
nai
None
There's none
nai
None
waraenai janai
No room to laugh
Using her quick wit and natural toughness, Emilyko manages
to save Kate. But they do not have time to celebrate their
reunion, as the soot glass shows the very little time remaining.
Will the two of them be able to reach the exit and pass the
Debut...? And what will the Shadow Family's goal turn out
to be...?
Using her quick wit and natural toughness, Emilyko manages
to save Kate. But they do not have time to celebrate their
reunion, as the soot glass shows the very little time remaining.
Will the two of them be able to reach the exit and pass the
Debut...? And what will the Shadow Family's goal turn out
to be...?
Emilyko is filled with loyalty towards the Shadow Family by drinking
the special coffee. Kate is shocked at her behavior, and manages to
relieve the brainwashing using information from the notebook in
Emilyko's room. Then Kate grabs the exhausted Emilyko's hand and
confides all her secrets to her.
Emilyko is filled with loyalty towards the Shadow Family by drinking
the special coffee. Kate is shocked at her behavior, and manages to
relieve the brainwashing using information from the notebook in
Emilyko's room. Then Kate grabs the exhausted Emilyko's hand and
confides all her secrets to her.
Next Episode
The Dark Drink
[KATE] Next episode,
"The Dark Drink."