To The Great Grandfather's Wing
Who are you?
What do you want with me?
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD] Tea truly
is an elegant beverage,
don't you agree?
Simply pour boiling water upon
the leaves, replace the lid,
and patiently let it brew.
The key is not to be hasty.
When the time is right,
stir ever so gently,
and pour the precious liquid
through the strainer.
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD] Finally,
enjoy the aroma, and take a sip.
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
Mm. That is how an adult
drinks their tea.
[EMILICO grunts]
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
Are you not thirsty?
Yes, a little.
Well then, let us prepare you
a cup with plenty of sugar.
If you'll cooperate
and share what you know.
Your mistress is quite
the malcontent, is she not?
Tell me, what is
Kate attempting to do?
[EMILICO growls]
I have nothing to say to you
about Mistress Kate! Besides,
not even knowing who you are,
I would never say a word to
anyone without her permission.
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
Is that so?
So, don't bother threatening me!
I can go a very long time
without drinking anything!
[stomach growls]
[EMILICO gulps]
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
Hmph.
Oh, darn. I guess I really
should've finished
that roll before I left.
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD] You lack
a sense of apprehension.
[EDWARD]
But there's plenty of time.
Come morning, I will expose
everything and present it
before Lord Grandfather.
[JOHN]
Yes, we need to find Edward,
but he lives in Lord
Grandfather's wing.
Are we really going
to have to sneak in there?
[PATRICK] Hmm, is such
a thing even possible?
[LOUISE]
Actually, perhaps not.
[JOHN] Could you take this
a bit more seriously?!
[LOUISE] It's not like
you've come up with
any brilliant ideas!
[JOHN] Uh. It's just...
nothing's come to mind yet.
[KATE sighs]
Oh, Shaun.
[JOHN] Hmm?
How may I be of service?
[KATE]
Do you have any ideas?
You're always so calm and
observant. Full of insight.
At least,
that's what Emilico says.
Please, tell us your thoughts.
[JOHN]
You know, she's right!
You really are a smart one
to have around, aren't you?
[SHAUN]
Hmm...
Yes, very well. Please allow
me a moment to think.
[SHAUN]
All right, come on now, think.
How can we get into
Lord Grandfather's wing
without anyone noticing?
I have nothing
to go on, no way to plan.
That wing of the manor is
a complete mystery to me.
There may even be traps
of some sort, for all I know.
[SHAUN] The main corridor is
the sole entrance I'm aware of,
so that may be our only option.
But what can we do
about the veiled dolls
that constantly stand guard?
[SHAUN gasps]
[JOHN]
Shaun?
Got it. There is a way.
One that's proven successful.
[EMILICO grunting]
That's so yummy!
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
What are you doing there?
Oh, just eating a roll.
You are a stubborn one.
How much longer can you
keep up this charade?
I don't need to now.
'Cause I'm not hungry anymore!
Remember, there's a way to
be freed from your bonds.
All that's required is for you
to reveal Kate's intentions.
The answer is still no!
Then remain as you are.
I say no to that, too!
Well, then, what of Kate's...
I said no!
Do you understand
the situation you're in?
[EMILICO snoring]
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
Are you even listening?!
[gasps]
Sorry, I guess I got sleepy.
It happens when I'm this full.
Hey! I know! Let's have
a nice conversation!
Because, really, I can't imagine
that you're doing this
because you want to.
I can't talk about Mistress
Kate, but I'm happy to listen
to anything you have to say!
There's lots we can chat about!
And that is certainly
more fun than this!
[sighs] You're going to be
the death of me.
[EDWARD]
Calm yourself, Edward.
Breathe. This isn't
that difficult.
[SHAUN] We should be able
to slip into the other wing
through this connecting
corridor right over here.
We're going to have to disguise
ourselves as veiled dolls.
[JOHN]
Oh, yes! Of course!
That's how Edward
pulled it off, so we will, too!
Very impressive, Shaun!
You're so perceptive!
Please, you're embarrassing me,
Master John.
[KATE]
Kate will go.
[JOHN grunts]
John will, too!
The more of us that go,
the greater the risk
of discovery will be.
[JOHN] Yes, but we still have
no idea where Emilico could be!
We must split up
and look for her...
[KATE]
That won't work.
We've no way
of maintaining contact.
Kate will go alone.
[JOHN growls]
[PATRICK] You're right,
but searching the entire wing
on your own sounds impossible.
[KATE]
Kate read a book about it.
The way it works in
Lord Grandfather's wing,
the higher the floor,
the more important
the shadows that live there.
So, there's a first,
second, and third floor.
I wonder which we're
likely to find Edward on.
[JOHN] The part John doesn't get
is why someone so important
would resort to sneaky
measures like an abduction.
[PATRICK]
True. It's quite devious.
[KATE]
Yes. Why take such a risk?
[LOUISE] Hold on! First, you'll
need to come up with a way
to steal a veiled
doll's uniform, won't you?
Do you have some
kind of plan for that?
[SHAUN]
Yes.
There must be a designated room
where they keep that sort of...
[knocking]
[GROUP gasping]
[LOUISE]
Who could that be at this hour?!
[BARBARA] Patrick, what's with
all the racket in there?
Open the door this instant!
[KATE]
Isn't that...?
[LOUISE]
It's Barbara!
[SHAUN]
You mean that Star Bearer?
[PATRICK]
Oh no... She must've heard us.
[KATE] We can escape
through Ricky's room.
[SHAUN]
But how?
Living dolls' rooms are
locked from the outside.
[JOHN] John will bust it
open himself if he must!
No, you can't!
If the lock is broken, they'll
suspect Patrick, for sure.
[knocking]
[BARBARA] How long will
you make Barbara wait?
Open this door now!
[LOUISE]
The time for thinking is over.
[PATRICK] Listen, let Patrick
and Ricky handle this.
The rest of you, just go!
[KATE]
All right. Thank you.
[BARBARA growls]
[PATRICK grunts]
Ricky, that chair.
[door clicks]
[PATRICK] Barbara! What brings
you here at this hour?
[BARBARA]
Don't play stupid.
Several voices were heard
coming from this room.
And as Barbara is a Star Bearer,
she is determined
to search every inch.
[PATRICK]
You must be mistaken.
[BARBARA] If that's the case,
you won't take issue
with being searched.
Barbie, go get to work.
[PATRICK whimpers]
[SHAUN grunts]
No use. It's locked.
[JOHN] Stand aside.
John'll break it down!
[KATE gasps]
Quiet!
[footsteps]
[LOUISE gasps]
[LOUISE] Hello, excuse me,
we need help over here!
[KATE]
Louise? What are you doing?!
[LOUISE]
Thank you for making the rounds.
[JOHN]
Huh? Who are you talking to?
[lock clicks]
[KATE, SHAUN gasps]
[LOUISE]
Now, let's get out of here.
[JOHN]
What just happened?
[LOUISE] Louise's soot
can control the dolls, silly.
Have you forgotten already?
[BARBIE]
There's no one else here.
[BARBARA] Interesting. That only
leaves the living doll's room.
[PATRICK grunts]
[BARBIE]
Hmm...
[JOHN]
So, what do we do now?!
We need to find
a uniform, for starters.
[LOUISE]
Not a problem!
Louise will simply make
the doll show us the way!
[KATE] All right.
Kate will go with you, Louise.
[JOHN]
What about John and Shaun?
[SHAUN]
Let's go assess the situation
over at the other wing.
Perhaps we'll find a way to
sneak in through there.
One can hope, anyway...
[JOHN] Great! Let's meet in
front of that corridor, Kate!
Sound good?
[KATE] Yes.
Make sure no one sees you.
There's nobody hiding in there.
[PATRICK]
It must've been our
heated conversation
you overheard! Apologies.
[BARBARA]
Hmph.
[PATRICK] So, since when have
you been on watch duty, anyway?
[BARBARA] After Edward
was put in charge of
the children's wing,
he told us to report any trouble
back to him, no matter
how small it may be.
[PATRICK]
Edward is in charge?
[BARBARA] Perhaps the debut
was well received.
[PATRICK]
Yes, so it seems.
But why report
such minor things?
[BARBARA] Oh, he's quite
the social climber.
It's infuriating!
[PATRICK gasps]
[BARBIE]
Mistress Barbara.
[BARBARA]
It is time for us to go.
Patrick, see that
you avoid actions
that may be deemed suspicious.
[PATRICK]
Y-Yes, ma'am!
[PATRICK sighs]
That was close...
But we did learn something
that might help Emilico.
[RICKY]
Why do this?
[PATRICK]
Hmm?
Why go out of your way
to help her? Some living doll?
[PATRICK gasps]
[PATRICK] Don't call her
"some living doll."
Her name is Emilico.
And you are Ricky.
[gasps]
[JOHN]
Well, there they are.
And if John has to...
No, please no punching,
Master John.
What if they were
to call for backup?
[JOHN]
Hmm?
The wings are a lot farther
apart than I thought,
and the cliff is high.
[JOHN] It's hard to see anything
when it's this dark.
We've only been over there once,
and that was just
because of the debut.
We'll have to try
and piece together
what it looks like inside,
but by relying on memory
and what we see from here.
[KATE]
How's this?
[LOUISE]
Yes! That's not bad at all!
[KATE]
What a relief.
[LOUISE] Well, this is
as far as Louise goes.
[KATE gasps]
[LOUISE] She couldn't possibly
risk herself further.
But best of luck to you, Kate!
[KATE]
Understood.
Thank you.
You've been a great help.
[LOUISE]
It was nothing.
Besides, Louise got a chance
to show off her soot power!
[KATE] Right, keep
your fingers crossed.
[LOUISE] Hmm.
What's the matter?
[LOUISE] This time,
it's Kate that he's after,
but that was just
luck of the draw.
His target could easily
have been Louise!
If that had happened, you would
have been abducted instead,
but Louise would
never let him touch you!
That no-good Edward
is loathsome!
[wheels creaking]
[SHAUN gasps]
[JOHN]
Oh no! They've found us!
Let's run for it!
[KATE]
Wait! It's Kate!
[JOHN gasps] Kate?!
Is it really?!
[SHAUN] All right, the first
floor of our wing connects
to the basement over in theirs.
So, once you manage
to get through the corridor,
you just need to find
the stairs that lead up.
[KATE]
Understood.
I would assume they have
watch duty over there as well.
But if it's only
some veiled dolls,
then I don't think they should
pose too much of a problem.
[JOHN] Perhaps,
but reaching the third floor
sounds nearly impossible.
[PATRICK]
There won't be a need for that.
[gasping]
[KATE]
Patrick! Ricky!
So glad you're safe.
[PATRICK] Barbara shared
a rather interesting tidbit.
Edward's in charge
of the children's wing,
and he seeks to rise to
the third floor. In short...
[KATE] ...he's on
the first or second floor!
[SHAUN] That's still a lot
of rooms, though.
It'd be impossible
to search them all.
[KATE]
Just leave it to Kate, Shaun.
She has an idea...
[PATRICK]
Don't bungle this.
We believe in you.
[KATE]
Thank you. We will make it back.
Both of us.
John's going to join you.
[SHAUN]
Master John!
[JOHN]
Doesn't this worry you sick?!
Just let John go instead!
[KATE] Mm-mm. No, you've
already done more than enough,
but thank you.
Thanks to the rest of you, too.
[KATE]
Time to go.
[JOHN whimpers]
It would appear that
she made it safely in.
[JOHN sighs]
[PATRICK] Well then, we should
all return to our rooms.
It'll spell trouble if
the watch finds us.
We ought to go,
as well. Shall we?
[JOHN]
All right...
[JOHN grunts]
Hmm...
[KATE]
This looks like one of the cups
they use for that coffee.
So this is where they make it.
[KATE] Nothing out of
the ordinary here.
Perhaps they alter it in
some way after they brew it.
[KATE grunts]
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
It's important that you know
I am doing this for
Kate's sake as well.
[EMILICO]
Mm?
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD] I want to
be of help before it's too late,
but it will require
your cooperation.
I don't... understand.
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
As it stands now,
Kate is to be discarded.
[EMILICO gasps]
Why, though?!
Because you,
my dear, are useless.
You are such a failure,
in fact, that Kate is unable
to advance any higher.
And that is why she rebels
against Shadows House.
It's akin to
a child's temper tantrum,
merely thrown out of spite.
I will not listen to you speak
ill of my Mistress Kate!
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD] Is there
nothing you can tell me?
After all, you're
always fretting over
trivial matters, right?
You like to ignore the rules.
It seems to me that you're
the one who led Kate down
the wrong path.
After all, you do disobey
the Shadow's House code.
But... I'm not...
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
Heh. Listen, dear.
I'm about to give you
a very unique opportunity.
All you have to do is
confess to everything,
and I shall help
Kate however I can.
[EMILICO whimpers]
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
I'm afraid you're the only one
who can save her now.
So, out with it.
Tell me, what is Kate planning?
[KATE gasps]
A cabinet of some sort?
Maybe... [gasps]
[KATE] Rolly, if you're
there, move for Kate.
Give Kate a sign.
[KATE] Let's try that again
with more conviction.
Emilico!
[KATE gasps]
[KATE]
Soot?
[gasps] No! Finding Emilico
is the only thing
that's important right now.
[gasps]
Rolly!
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
Hmm? Rolly? What is that?
[EMILICO]
Oh, nothing.
Mistress Kate...!
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD] Now, tell
me what that malcontent Kate
has up her sleeve.
You don't know her at all.
She's braver than anyone else,
and she's kinder, too.
And that's why she is
my beloved mistress!
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
Absurd!
[gasps]
[EMILICO gasps]
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD growls]
Goodness.
Just look at this mess.
[knocking]
[EMILICO gasps]
[EMILICO whimpers]
[VEILED SHADOW EDWARD]
Don't make a sound.
[KATE] Was that the cart
that was used to abduct Emilico?
[EDWARD]
Oh, it's you.
Is everything all right?
We thought we heard something.
[thud]
[AILEEN]
Huh?
[AILEEN] So you really did
take her, then.
[EDWARD]
Let's speak outside.
[EMILICO whimpers]
That sound.
A cup shattering.
Rolly must have crashed into it.
[EMILICO grunts]
[EMILICO] Mistress Kate wept
as she forced me to drink
glass after glass of water
so I could turn back
into myself again.
She called me Emilico so that
I could be my own person
instead of just an echo of her.
And she's ever kind,
always watching out for me,
even though I'm so
clumsy all the time!
[EMILICO groans]
I know Mistress Kate is here!
Come on, Mistress!
Where are you?!
[KATE]
All right. No one's here.
[KATE gasps]
[KATE]
Just stay calm.
[KATE sighs]
[GERALD]
Wait, where are you going?
[AILEEN] Well, Edward said
an intruder was coming,
so I thought I would
take a look around.
If they really are trying to
save that missing living doll,
they'll use a veiled-doll
disguise just like Edward did.
It's the only
logical thing to do.
[KATE gasps]
[AILEEN]
I'd be surprised if they weren't
pushing a cart as well.
Though I doubt they
could actually get it up
to the second floor.
[GERALD] So, the number of carts
in the basement should tell us
if they're here.
[KATE grunts]
[KATE]
I'm running out of time.
I need to rescue Emilico
before they return.
[KATE] Rolly, heed this
call if you're there.
Where is Emilico?
[KATE]
Please respond!
[EMILICO]
Mistress Kate!
[KATE gasps]
[EMILICO]
Mistress Kate!
[KATE]
Emilico!
[EMILICO]
In here! I'm in here!
[KATE]
Emilico?
Where? Where are you?!
[KATE]
There you are!
[EMILICO whimpering]
[KATE]
Are you all right?!
Let's take this off.
[gasps]
Mistress Kate!
[KATE] It's such a relief
to see you safe.
Let's get out of here.
[EMILICO]
Behind you, Mistress, look!
[KATE]
Behind me?
[EMILICO EDWARD] So, you've
arrived at last, I see.
[KATE gasps]
[EMILICO gasps]
[EDWARD]
Greetings, Mistress Kate.
hai no nai fukai kage bakari
Ashless shadows here and everywhere I look
I no nai kotai dooru mitai
Like dolls without a self to call their own
jibun fuzai dokonimo inai
I, myself, am absent all the same
nai janai
Utterly bereft
aimai na I iro no nai I
My nebulous, colorless self
gitai igai
This mimicry, a surprise!
hitogoto mitai
As if it's not my concern
okagesama dochira sama
"And who might you be, esteemed Shadow?"
kotae samazama
Varied were our answers
nanimono demo nai mama
If I lived without a self
nan ni mo dekinai mama
If I couldn't do a thing
ikiru no wa muda desu ka
Would my life still have meaning?
warui koto desu ka
Would that be so wrong?
koko ni inai inai
It's not here, it's gone
inai no wa jibun jibun
What's gone is me, is me
dare mo minai minai
They don't see me, see me
minai mama hakisutete sayounara
Unseen, I'll be swept away, goodbye
ureshikunai
Neither joy
kanashiku mo nai
Nor sorrow
toumei na kibun
My feelings, invisible
tarinai jibun awasu kao mo nai
I'm not enough, no face to show
nai
None
There's none
nai
None
waraenai janai
No room to laugh
Emilyko is abducted. Kate confers with John and the others,
and with an idea of who the culprit is, they decide to venture
to The Great Grandfather's Wing. With the cooperation of
everyone who overcame the Debut, they set foot into the
hallway of renown.
Emilyko is abducted. Kate confers with John and the others,
and with an idea of who the culprit is, they decide to venture
to The Great Grandfather's Wing. With the cooperation of
everyone who overcame the Debut, they set foot into the
hallway of renown.
Kate manages to find Emilyko, but
everything has already gone according to Edward's plan. If the two
of them cannot escape by morning, they will face punishment as
dissidents. In the midst of this hopeless situation, two shadows are
sneaking around... Will the two of them manage to escape Edward's
grasp?
Kate manages to find Emilyko, but
everything has already gone according to Edward's plan. If the two
of them cannot escape by morning, they will face punishment as
dissidents. In the midst of this hopeless situation, two shadows are
sneaking around... Will the two of them manage to escape Edward's
grasp?
Next Episode
For the Sake of the Shadow Family
[KATE] Next episode, "For the
Sake of the Shadows Family."