[KATE] Rolly, heed this call
if you're there.
Where is Emilico?
[KATE]
Please respond!
[EMILICO]
Mistress Kate!
[KATE gasps]
[EMILICO]
Mistress Kate!
[KATE]
Emilico!
[EMILICO]
In here! I'm in here!
[KATE]
Emilico? Where?
Where are you?
[KATE]
There you are!
[EMILICO grunting]
[KATE] Are you all right?
Let's take this off.
[EMILICO gasps]
Mistress Kate!
[KATE] It's such a relief
to see you safe.
Let's get out of here.
[EMILICO]
Behind you, Mistress, look!
[KATE]
Behind me?
[EDWARD (EMILICO)] So, you've
arrived at last, I see.
[KATE gasps]
[gasps]
Greetings, Mistress Kate.
Hello, Edward.
[EDWARD] Hmm. Well, this was
most definitely worth the wait.
I had no doubt you
would come, of course.
It's quite obvious you're
a shadow who truly cares
for her doll.
So it was Kate who you
were after all along.
[chuckles]
Come morning, I'll take you
before Lord Grandfather
and expose you
for what you are...
A malcontent enemy
of Shadows House.
Then, I'll likely rise
to the third floor...
My long-cherished wish.
[KATE growls]
[EDWARD]
So, Kate... answer me this.
What is it you're planning
in that head of yours?
I should mention, if you think
you'll get away with this
by not responding
to the question,
I'm afraid you are mistaken.
Whether malcontent or no, it's
clear you've broken other rules.
For instance, here you are,
dressed as a veiled doll
in Lord Grandfather's wing.
Kate is only here to save
Emilico, whom you abducted...
[EDWARD] Do you honestly
think he would take
your word for that?
I'm a trusted adult,
and you're but a child.
I'd say it's fairly
obvious which of us
Lord Grandfather would believe.
[EDWARD] The outcome
of our battle was decided
from the start, Kate.
Now all that remains
is for us to wait patiently
for Lord Grandfather
to wake and do his will.
A harsh penalty,
no doubt, awaits you.
This may well be
your last cup of tea.
[EMILICO gasps]
Best say your prayers.
It's all over for you.
[JOHN grunts]
[JOHN] Hold on, Kate.
John's coming for you!
[JOHN growls]
For the Sake of the Shadow Family
What floor was it again?
[JOHN gasps]
Who are you?
[JOHN] What?! Go away,
you creepy little thing!
John... I mean, I am seeking
the room that belongs to Edward.
[JOHN]
You want me to follow you?
Who would fall for something...
[gasps]
There were two
extra carts, Aileen.
That means two intruders
in Lord Grandfather's wing.
Then let's keep our eyes peeled.
I will see that
Edward is informed.
They must be disguised
as veiled dolls.
There's no other way they
could have made it this far.
[AILEEN] Uh?
[GERALD] Huh?
[JOHN] Don't mind me! I shall
go search for the intruders!
[AILEEN]
It spoke.
[JOHN gasps]
[JOHN groans]
[AILEEN]
Get back here!
[JOHN panting]
Now you won't be
causing any more trouble.
[thud]
[EDWARD] Hmm?
[EMILICO gasps]
Not a sound.
[KATE gasps]
It's adorable!
Edward,
There were two wagons, so two intruders
We're chasing one of them
[EDWARD] I'll be the one
to expose them all
for the troublemakers they are.
An act that will finally
secure my advancement
to the coveted third floor.
[EDWARD]
Are we behaving ourselves?
It appears you've
conceded defeat.
Very wise, as it's foolish
to defy Shadows House.
But it's too late
to rue your mistake.
Dear me, it looks
as though your last cup of tea
has gone cold.
Oh, forgive me.
You can't drink it
in your present state.
[gasps]
[KATE grunts]
[EDWARD gasps]
[KATE]
Now!
[EDWARD gasps]
[grunts]
What the...?!
[KATE]
Emilico!
[EMILICO grunts]
[EDWARD]
Hey! Wait!
[KATE, EMILICO panting]
[JOHN panting]
[KATE gasps]
[KATE]
No, it's John.
[EMILICO]
Master John!
[KATE]
You came to save us.
[JOHN]
Naturally!
But at the moment,
John could use some help.
[footsteps]
[BOTH gasp]
[KATE]
What should we do now?
[EMILICO]
Oh?
[JOHN]
You again?!
[KATE]
She's on our side. Hurry!
[PATRICK]
Hmm? So? Did you find John?
[SHAUN] No. But I believe
that's because he went to
the other wing in order
to save Mistress Kate.
[PATRICK]
Of all the harebrained ideas.
Let's hope he doesn't
do more harm than good.
Hold on, what of Louise and Lou?
They returned to their rooms.
They were tired.
[PATRICK]
Well, you are no help at all.
If it had gone as planned, they
would already be back by now.
Hmm... Most worrisome.
I'm truly sorry it's
causing you such concern.
However, I have
complete confidence in
Master John's abilities.
There's no doubt he'll
return safely with those two.
Though I'm sure Edward
will make it difficult.
[RICKY] Hmm. Then that
will be Patrick's cue
to spring into action.
[PATRICK]
You think Patrick can stop him?
[RICKY]
Oh... No, i-it's just...
My apologies for
being so incompetent.
[RICKY groans]
[SHAUN sighs]
[RICKY] Master Patrick,
you may not see it,
but your desire to save
your friends is evidence
of your kindness and strength.
[PATRICK gasps]
In my opinion, the greatest
power you possess is what
comes out of your brave
and beautiful heart.
[PATRICK gulps]
Heh. Well, if that's so,
then it's because of you.
During the debut, you tearfully
pleaded with John and Shaun
to take care of Patrick,
and here I am.
I'll never forget it.
[RICKY]
Thank you, Master...
[GROUP panting]
[KATE]
The roof?
[JOHN]
Wait a minute...
It wants us to
escape by jumping?!
[KATE gasps]
[KATE]
Our wing is pretty far.
[EDWARD]
Now I have you!
[GROUP gasps]
[KATE gasps]
[JOHN grunts]
There's no point resisting,
I assure you.
This is the end of your story.
You have defied the House.
By entering Grandfather's wing
without permission.
[JOHN] Yes, but you trespassed
in the children's wing first!
Who will believe
your word over mine?
Don't be ridiculous.
[AILEEN chuckles]
[JOHN groans]
[EDWARD laughs]
[JOHN groans, gasps]
Kate! Take Emilico and jump!
[KATE]
What about you, John?!
Just go already!
[EDWARD] Hey, why are you
still flapping your gums?
[EMILICO gasps]
[KATE]
Emilico...
Hold on tight.
All right!
Give it up, Kate...
Don't be silly.
There's no way your soot power
can carry you that far.
[EMILICO gasps]
So they've decided they prefer
to plunge to their deaths.
A fitting end for
a foolish malcontent.
[JOHN]
That's what you think!
[bellows]
[GERALD grunts]
[JOHN] John is not about
to let Kate perish!
[EMILICO gasps]
[EDWARD gasps]
[JOHN]
Don't you ever underestimate
John and his friends...
[sighs]
[EDWARD snarls]
Aileen, quickly!
[JOHN snarls]
[GERALD grunts]
[JOHN] John is not about
to let Kate perish!
[EMILICO gasps]
[EDWARD gasps]
[KATE grunts]
I fear we might not make it.
Mistress Kate,
will you forgive me?
Having to carry me like this...
It's a terrible burden
for you, I know it is,
and for Master John, too.
[KATE] Don't think like that.
Now is not the time.
[EMILICO]
Ah!
[KATE]
Emilico, try to be still!
Sorry, I will.
[PATRICK]
So something did go wrong.
This is obviously
the only way in or out.
[SHAUN gasps]
Look!
[GROUP gasping]
[PATRICK]
What on earth...?
Mistress Kate! Emilico!
We're over here!
[SHAUN]
Slowly now! Don't panic!
[EMILICO gasps]
Oh, no!
[EMILICO grunts]
[groaning]
Ah!
[BOTH gasp]
[PATRICK panting]
You're safe...
No, not yet!
[SHAUN]
Edward...
Run for it!
[GROUP panting]
[PATRICK]
Kate, what happened to John?
[KATE] He used his soot power
to propel our flight,
but Kate fears that doing so
may have prevented him
from escaping himself.
[SHAUN grunts]
[shrill squealing]
[KATE]
Ah!
No! Mistress Kate!
[KATE groaning]
[KATE]
Edward...
You've been nothing but trouble!
[EMILICO whimpers]
[PATRICK] You're in
the children's wing now!
We won't just let you come in
and do as you please!
You're an infant!
You can't challenge one of my
standing here or anywhere else!
If you wish to survive here
in Shadows House,
dispense with this inane
sense of friendship!
And as for you, dear,
surrender to your fate!
[KATE grunts]
[EDWARD] The rest of you,
if you continue to bar my way,
I'll discard you all!
[BARBARA]
What exactly does that mean?
[gasps]
[EDWARD gasps]
[PATRICK]
So, uh, you didn't go to bed?
[LOUISE]
Change of plans.
Calling Barbara was
a fine idea, was it not?
Now Louise is sure
to be a Star Bearer!
[PATRICK]
Louise will be Louise.
[BARBARA]
How strange.
You live in Lord Grandfather's
wing, do you not, Edward?
Yet here you are
in the children's wing.
[SUSANNA]
What is the meaning of all this?
Do explain yourself.
I'm instructing them firsthand!
That is my job, after all.
[BENJAMIN] What sort of
instruction is done at daybreak?
[OLIVER] And how is a threat
to discard these children
in any way instructive?
[EDWARD growls]
[BARBARA] Even as caretaker,
unauthorized entry to
the Children's wing is forbidden
to you, as you're well aware.
The third-floor lords have
already been informed
of this violation.
[EDWARD]
What is this?!
[BARBARA] They await you
at the end of the corridor.
[EDWARD gasps]
[BARBARA] This is really
all thanks to you.
You so kindly... and rightly,
it would seem... instructed us
to watch over this wing
with great care each day.
In the end, that's what
allowed us to expose
your egregious misconduct.
We are very grateful.
[EDWARD growls]
[EDWARD]
Please forgive me.
I am truly sorry
for what I have done.
[RYAN] Oh, it's far too late to
bow down and say you're sorry.
Edward, you are hereby
banished from Shadows House.
Banished, you say, me?
[DOROTHY]
Well, naturally.
You claim you were
instructing the children,
yet far from teaching them,
you entered their wing
for the purpose of abduction.
[EDWARD]
No, that was...
[RYAN]
You dare to question us?
You became a liability
by making the faces fret
over trivial matters
at the debut.
You're done. Shadows House
no longer has any use for you.
[SOPHIE] It only needs those
who can be of true service
to Lord Grandfather.
[DOROTHY]
Yes, Edward should be banished.
As for the other two, how about
a demotion to the first floor?
[RYAN]
Excellent. It's settled, then.
[GERALD, AILEEN whimper]
[JOSEPH]
What say you, Lord?
[LORD GRANDFATHER] Edward,
your bold and unique instruction
of the children has been of
great interest to us, of course.
However, it seems you have
carried it a bit too far.
We hereby give all three of you
the sternest of all
possible reprimands.
[DOROTHY, RYAN gasp]
[EDWARD sighs]
You got that?
This is your last chance.
Yes. And now, I shall
devote myself body and soul.
[RYAN] Were we not too lenient,
Lord Grandfather?
[LORD GRANDFATHER]
Don't concern yourself.
The unrealized potential
of Shadows House is manifold.
[chuckles]
That was a little
too close for comfort.
Not to mention, this puts
the third floor further away.
Edward, you must cease
your self-indulgent ways.
I have not yet
given up on my goal.
I sense a great love
for me in what he said.
That magnanimous
judgment meant something.
I am determined
to repay that debt.
And I will.
I hereby vow to get rid of those
fiendish malcontents,
right along with
all the grasping,
petty third-floor maggots.
[EDWARD] Everything I do is for
the sake of Lord Grandfather!
[bell tolling]
[EMILICO giggles]
[KATE]
What is it, Emilico?
Well, it's just kind of hard to
believe we're allowed to venture
outside our rooms so openly.
It's such an unexpected joy
walking by your side like this.
[KATE]
Is it?
[EMILICO]
But I do wonder...
What do you think happened to
Master John after we escaped?
[KATE] Unfortunately,
that is still unknown.
[EMILICO groans]
[SARAH]
Bad form!
As the newest of the bunch,
you should have been here first.
[KATE] Apologies.
Everyone arrived so fast.
John! You're safe and sound!
[JOHN] Indeed! John hung on
for his poor, dear life,
to the tail of Edward's
soot pigeon, that is!
John's here thanks to
that strange little creature.
[KATE]
How interesting.
[EMILICO giggles]
[PATRICK]
Hmph.
[KATE] Come to think of it,
where's Louise?
[LOUISE humming]
[MARYROSE]
O Kate, most beauteous rose!
And Louise, daisy in full bloom!
Let the orientation begin.
You shall now learn how to lead
proper lives at the manor!
[KATE]
Thank you very much.
[LOUISE]
All ready here!
Mistress Kate,
I've been wondering,
what do you suppose
that thing was?
[KATE]
What thing?
[EMILICO] That cute little
creature that helped us.
I haven't been able to stop
thinking about it since.
[KATE]
Yes, that what quite unusual.
For one thing, how did it
come to know so much
about Kate's soot powers?
Mistress Kate?
Is something the matter?
[KATE]
Perhaps...
Patterns in Soot Powers
[train whistle blows]
[CHILDREN]
Let us ever remember.
The Shadows are
an exceptional noble family,
and to serve them is
the pride and joy of
every living doll's existence.
[LORD GRANDFATHER]
One must never forget
one's eternal gratitude...
to Shadows House.
♪
[SHAUN]
♪ Though today, we clean away ♪
Soot will gather again ♪
♪ So we let it pile up
And we clean more then ♪
♪ Now, hurry and
let's get to work! ♪
♪ Make ourselves useful
and show our worth! ♪
♪ Trivial matters need no fuss,
we'll be good as can be ♪
[music ends abruptly]
All for the Shadows family.
hai no nai fukai kage bakari
Ashless shadows here and everywhere I look
I no nai kotai dooru mitai
Like dolls without a self to call their own
jibun fuzai dokonimo inai
I, myself, am absent all the same
nai janai
Utterly bereft
aimai na I iro no nai I
My nebulous, colorless self
gitai igai
This mimicry, a surprise!
hitogoto mitai
As if it's not my concern
okagesama dochira sama
"And who might you be, esteemed Shadow?"
kotae samazama
Varied were our answers
nanimono demo nai mama
If I lived without a self
nan ni mo dekinai mama
If I couldn't do a thing
ikiru no wa muda desu ka
Would my life still have meaning?
warui koto desu ka
Would that be so wrong?
koko ni inai inai
It's not here, it's gone
inai no wa jibun jibun
What's gone is me, is me
dare mo minai minai
They don't see me, see me
minai mama hakisutete sayounara
Unseen, I'll be swept away, goodbye
ureshikunai
Neither joy
kanashiku mo nai
Nor sorrow
toumei na kibun
My feelings, invisible
tarinai jibun awasu kao mo nai
I'm not enough, no face to show
nai
None
There's none
nai
None
waraenai janai
No room to laugh