[EMILICO] ♪ Now, hurry,
and let's get to work ♪
[KATE] Emilico, when you
first arrived here...
it was clear to me that you
served the Shadows family
without question.
There was no way
I could trust you.
But now I can see that
it was because of
the coffee, wasn't it?
And then, at the debut, you
were forced to drink it again...
just when you were beginning
to regain a true sense
of who you really are.
[KATE] I know Emilico is the
type who keeps everything,
so there should be some
sort of a hint in her room.
[KATE] I will get you back,
I swear that to you,
my dearly beloved Emilico.
The Dark Drink
[KATE]
"The Shadow Family's Teachings.
One must study this
book to learn the rules
by which to live."
Let's see...
"Before the debut, shadows may
not interact with others.
Lord Grandfather is absolute,
never to be questioned.
Always have your
living doll with you.
Cherish your contact
with your living doll.
Maintain your dignity as a
master while ever-improving
the chemistry with your face."
It also provides some
useful information on
the house's different
wings and the Star Bearers.
[KATE] As for soot, there's
asection on how it's emitted
due to negative feelings
and how scorches spawn
if you don't clean,
but that's about it.
There are certainly other books,
too, but they only explain
how to become
a more cultured noble.
They don't teach
children anything
about what's really important.
[KATE] The living doll's manual
primarily emphasizes loyalty
to Shadows House and
the importance of serving
as a living doll.
It also covers scorches...
but it doesn't appear
Emilico read that far.
[KATE]
That should be hanging up.
[KATE grunts]
[KATE] She always used
to keep this in her pocket.
[KATE] I feel sorry
for you, too, little one.
May you one day
play with Emilico again.
[KATE gasps]
[KATE giggles]
Quite the crash landing.
[KATE gasps]
Thoughts
[KATE]
"'Don't Fret' Notebook"?
Thoughts
Emilico kept something
hidden from me?
Forgive me, but I must read it.
[EMILICO] This notebook is my
special place for writing down
all the things I should
not be thinking about,
so then I can forget about them.
[KATE giggles] Wouldn't
writing them down make her
remember them even more?
That's just like her.
"Major cleaning
of the Great Hall
with the other living dolls.
My team members were
Mia, Rosemary, and Lou."
Are these even things she
should've been thinking about?
[EMILICO] I guess I might as
well use this as a diary, too.
[KATE chuckles]
She's justifying it.
The phantom mayhem that Emilico
told me about isn't mentioned
at all in "The Shadow
Family's Teachings."
[gasps]
"Night watch duty"?
So, she had to do
that as punishment?
I really wish she would've
just told me the truth.
[EMILICO] I didn't want
Mistress Kate to get angry,
so I kept it a secret.
[KATE]
Hey, now!
That makes me sound like
I have a bad disposition!
[KATE]
Mm.
[KATE gasps]
Soot sickness...?
One simply drinks lots of water?
That's how Rosemary was cured?
So, you want me
to drink this water?
[KATE]
That's right.
And you'll do whatever
makes Kate happy, won't you?
Yes, of course!
[KATE] Based on what
she says in her notebook...
soot sickness seems to be
a sort of mental illness,
and those who drink
the coffee fall into a state
of extreme loyalty
which defies all reason.
The symptoms may differ
slightly, but they are both
forms of insanity...
A takeover of the mind.
One can't be sure, of course,
but that coffee was most likely
doctored with soot.
Uh, thanks, but I don't
think I can drink any more.
[KATE sighs]
Yes, you can... go on.
[EMILICO gasps]
[KATE] What was the point
of hiding the truth about soot
from us younger shadows?
[KATE] Is it because if we
knew about soot sickness...
and noticed how
our dolls change after
drinking the coffee, we might
empathize and try to cure them?
[EMILICO retches]
[splattering]
[KATE gasps]
[EMILICO panting]
[KATE]
Emilico...
How do you feel about...
what happened to Rum?
Mistress Kate, why are
you asking me this now...?
[KATE]
Keep drinking.
All right, yes...
[KATE]
I can't just let you forget.
You had regained such a strong
sense of yourself, Emilico.
[KATE grunts]
[grunting]
[KATE]
Please.
Forgive me!
[EMILICO retches]
[coughs]
[KATE gasps]
[gasps]
[EMILICO whimpers]
[sobbing]
[KATE gasps]
That's enough!
[sobbing continues]
[KATE] You don't have
to drink any more, okay?!
Please forgive Kate!
That must've been difficult!
[EMILICO] It's not that...
I don't understand...
I remember...
I remember what happened
in the debut hall!
I can't believe it...
and I'm so sad...
But...
no matter how much
I think about that day,
the only feelings that
come are those of joy.
[sobs]
But how...?
How could I feel joy when Rum
is no longer here with us...?
[sobs]
She tried so hard...
It's too much to bear...!
[sobbing]
[KATE]
Feel better now?
Yes, ma'am.
[KATE]
No, you should rest.
Listen, Emilico.
Kate is going to tell you
something that must remain
only between us.
[gasps]
[train whistle blows]
[RYAN]
Such a tedious task.
[DOROTHY]
We must all take our turn.
And anyway, is it not
a delight to portray fine,
handsome nobles,
beloved by the people?
[VILLAGER 11A]
It's the soot train!
[VILLAGER 11B]
That means visitors from
the Shadows Family!
[VILLAGER 11C] I trust the
offerings are all prepared?
Goodness me, the air's thick
enough to cut with a knife.
And while it isn't as dense
as Lord Grandfather's soot,
it is nonetheless effective
at preventing the mind
from working properly,
thus rendering the villagers
delightfully susceptible
to our manipulation.
There's plenty of
soot coal for you,
so do try to make
good use of it.
Thank you for this fine gift.
We've eagerly awaited it.
[RYAN]
Well then, let's get to it.
Right. This way,
if you please, my lord.
[gasps]
Come now, no need to be
so nervous, my dear.
[RYAN]
What a fine complexion you have.
[DOROTHY] Let us choose
more girls this time, shall we?
[DOROTHY] Today, the
prestigious assignments will go
to these three.
This is the ceremony
for entering our manor.
Now... best drink it all.
[giggling]
[DOROTHY chuckles]
A little bitter, isn't it?
Well done, dears.
The Shadows family is
pleased to welcome you.
You can bid your own
families goodbye knowing
how proud they are.
How lucky to have had
a daughter who was chosen.
Oh, yes. We're grateful for the
life of privilege she'll lead,
working at the great house.
[VILLAGER 11B] What would we
ever do without the manor?
The joyous birth of some
brand-new shadows draws near!
May you all become fine,
young living dolls.
[KATE] There are several
villages surrounding the manor.
You were born in one of them,
but your memory was erased
before you were brought
here to Shadows House.
[KATE]
Emilico, you are a human child.
[gasps]
[KATE] Shadows House
has wronged us all.
For both shadows
and living dolls,
this place is nothing
more than a prison.
[KATE]
It must be bewildering.
[EMILICO]
Uh...
Uh. May I, um...
Could I please borrow a mirror?
Wah! I've always wanted
to see a human!
This is great!
So that's how they look!
It's just exactly
like a living doll!
[KATE] No, you weren't
really listening.
There is no such thing
as a living doll.
[EMILICO]
Oh, right, sorry!
[EMILICO] It's all
a little confusing, but...
I believe you,
Mistress Kate! I promise!
[KATE gasps]
And if all of us
are human, then...
I would like to help everyone
return to their villages!
[EMILICO]
Hmm!
Ah...!
[knocking]
[EMILICO]
Huh...?
[KATE]
Emilico, a word, please.
Where did you go?
[JOHN]
It was before the debut.
[JOHN] John saw a living
doll go tumbling down
while gazing out the window.
Hoping to see more, John snuck
outside without Shaun noticing.
[KATE] You tried to protect
that which you treasure.
That's good progress.
[JOHN]
It's strange...
and sort of
difficult to explain,
but John fell for Kate
at that moment!
[JOHN] If you would ever
consider getting engaged,
please come to John's room.
[JOHN gasps]
[door latch clicks]
[KATE panting]
[JOHN]
Ah! You actually came!
Does this mean you've
decided to accept...
[KATE]
John, Emilico is gone!
[JOHN]
Huh?
[KATE] Kate has freed her
from their brainwashing.
[JOHN]
Is this a joke?
No.
Please, listen carefully.
The living dolls
aren't dolls at all.
They're human children.
And they've been brainwashed
by Shadows House.
[JOHN]
Wait, this is outrageous!
The living dolls are
brainwashed humans?!
Are you sure?
[KATE]
Yes, it's true!
And what's more,
after Kate freed Emilico's mind
and told her the truth
about herself,
she vanished without a trace.
[JOHN]
So, Shaun... he's a human, too?
[KATE]
Mm.
[thudding]
[JOHN gasps]
[SHAUN] I'm finished
cleaning the bathroom.
[KATE]
John, think.
You must've noticed Shaun
acting a bit differently.
[JOHN]
Differently?
Say, Shaun, why are you
wearing those glasses?
They allow me to do
my work more efficiently.
Of course, I'll remove them
outside of your room.
[JOHN] You said you'd always try
to match the way John looked.
As you wish, then, sir.
[JOHN]
Why're you so... compliant?!
You could at least argue
with John a little bit!
You're the same as
you were when we first met.
[JOHN sighs]
Come to think of it,
Shaun often used
to lecture John, didn't he?
But he doesn't do that anymore.
What's this forlorn feeling?
It's as if his
heart's gone cold.
Shaun, you know that you don't
have to pledge your loyalty
to Shadows House, don't you?
[SHAUN] Master...
Shadows House is absolute!
[JOHN grunts] Shaun,
you've never glared at John
like that before!
What's wrong?!
You have to snap out of it!
[KATE] Please, calm down!
[JOHN] Listen, Shaun.
Emilico has disappeared!
That's right,
you should be shocked!
It's the worst kind of news!
John is going to look for her.
And he's going
with or without you!
You know that it's forbidden
for you to leave your room
without your living doll.
[JOHN] What?! When did you
become so coldhearted?
[snarls]
[KATE]
John, stop it!
Mistress Kate?
What are you doing here?
[JOHN]
No, let go of me, Kate!
We're going to have to
settle this, man to man!
Please, stop this!
My face will get...
Ahh!
[JOHN growls]
Who cares about your face?!
All John wants is to have
the old Shaun back!
Look at John!
[sobs]
John's crying...!
Do you know why? Because
John's heart aches inside!
[SHAUN gasps]
[JOHN growls]
Stop, no!
[SHAUN grunts]
I'm the only one
feeling pain here!
[JOHN groans]
[gasps]
[JOHN]
Now that's the real Shaun!
However...
it's still not enough!
[growls]
[grunts]
[grunting, groaning]
[groans]
[BOTH growl]
[KATE gasps]
[BOTH panting]
I've failed as a
living doll, haven't I?
To have done something so
foolish, and to my master...
[footsteps]
[JOHN] You know why?
Because you're human, Shaun.
[SHAUN]
Mm.
[SHAUN grunts]
[LOUISE] Now where could
that Kate have gone?
Louise had something
simply wonderful she was
planning to show her.
[LOUISE]
What are you doing there?!
[KATE, JOHN]
Louise!
[LOUISE]
You are both just awful!
You were deliberately trying
to exclude Louise, weren't you?
[JOHN] No! We were
in a hurry, that's all!
[PATRICK] Take your
silly quarrel elsewhere.
[KATE]
Forgive the sudden intrusion.
But... there's something
that you need to hear.
[PATRICK] Wait, what do
you mean, Emilico is gone?
[KATE]
It's true.
Please... I'm begging you,
help Kate look for her!
[LOUISE]
Who was Emilico, again?
[KATE] She's Kate's
beloved living doll.
[LOUISE]
Interesting. What an odd name.
But enough about that!
Just look!
Louise wanted to find you
so she could show you this.
[KATE gasps]
[LOUISE]
Sad face...
Happiest face in the world!
Fabulous, isn't it?
Louise has complete control!
[KATE] My power is physical,
but it seems that there are also
powers that affect the mind.
[PATRICK] Hold on. What exactly
do you mean by "control?"
[KATE gasps] Kate will explain
later. That's a promise.
Unfortunately, now is
just not the time.
Louise, were you even
listening to a word Kate said?
[LOUISE]
Of course.
You were talking
about your living doll.
Oh, yes! Speaking of dolls,
Louise noticed a surprisingly
tall veiled doll when she
was making her way here.
It was pushing a cart with
a big bundle on it shaped like
a living doll.
[KATE]
A living doll... on a cart?
[LOUISE] And being
the clever shadow she is,
Louise figured out who it was!
[JOHN]
So? Who was it?
[LOUISE]
You mean you can't guess?
[KATE gasps]
[EMILICO whimpers]
[EMILICO grunting, groaning]
Please, tell me who you are!
And why you've
abducted me like this!
[VEILED SHADOW]
Greetings.
I hope you'll forgive
the heavy-handed tactics.
[EMILICO] Who are you?
Please take this off!
I can't see a thing!
[VEILED SHADOW]
The tea leaves are dancing about
as if they feel the heat.
You must start by pouring
boiling water most vigorously
if you wish to brew
the finest tea.
[EMILICO] Please answer me!
Who are you?!
Why are you doing this?!
What do you want?!
[VEILED SHADOW]
Now, all there is to do is wait.
[JOHN]
Edward abducted Emilico?!
[LOUISE] His ridiculous suit
was just visible under his robe.
Edward is the only one
who wears such vulgar attire.
[KATE]
There can be no doubt.
Edward mistrusts Kate.
It makes sense, as Kate
hid her soot power from him
until the debut.
He's likely trying to figure out
where Kate's loyalties lie.
If they belong to
Shadows House or not.
[JOHN]
He's pigheaded, all right.
That lout didn't even bother to
tell John the labyrinth's rules,
so his clothes ended up
getting all dirty!
You should've seen Shaun's
downcast face when he saw that!
[LOUISE]
Louise detests Edward, too!
Those awful trees he used
in the labyrinth were
full of thorns... Thorns!
They could have scratched up
Lou's beautiful face
and then where would she be?
[PATRICK] Ricky suffered
even worse than you.
Edward actually attempted
to crush him with
an enormous boulder!
[KATE] And there's no doubt that
Shirley's failure at the debut
was Edward's doing!
[PATRICK grunts]
Patrick will help you find her.
[KATE gasps]
[LOUISE] Louise will gladly lend
a hand, if for no other reason
than to spite Edward.
[KATE]
Thank you...
[JOHN] There's no question
the living dolls were
a great help at the debut.
It's time the shadows
repay that debt.
[KATE gasps]
[KATE]
Now that that's settled,
we'll need to move quickly.
We're dealing with
Edward, after all.
Who knows what he's
capable of doing to her?
[KATE]
Emilico...
hai no nai fukai kage bakari
Ashless shadows here and everywhere I look
I no nai kotai dooru mitai
Like dolls without a self to call their own
jibun fuzai dokonimo inai
I, myself, am absent all the same
nai janai
Utterly bereft
aimai na I iro no nai I
My nebulous, colorless self
gitai igai
This mimicry, a surprise!
hitogoto mitai
As if it's not my concern
okagesama dochira sama
"And who might you be, esteemed Shadow?"
kotae samazama
Varied were our answers
nanimono demo nai mama
If I lived without a self
nan ni mo dekinai mama
If I couldn't do a thing
ikiru no wa muda desu ka
Would my life still have meaning?
warui koto desu ka
Would that be so wrong?
koko ni inai inai
It's not here, it's gone
inai no wa jibun jibun
What's gone is me, is me
dare mo minai minai
They don't see me, see me
minai mama hakisutete sayounara
Unseen, I'll be swept away, goodbye
ureshikunai
Neither joy
kanashiku mo nai
Nor sorrow
toumei na kibun
My feelings, invisible
tarinai jibun awasu kao mo nai
I'm not enough, no face to show
nai
None
There's none
nai
None
waraenai janai
No room to laugh
Emilyko is filled with loyalty towards the Shadow Family by
drinking the special coffee. Kate is shocked at her behavior,
and manages to relieve the brainwashing using information
from the notebook in Emilyko's room. Then Kate grabs the
exhausted Emilyko's hand and confides all her secrets to her.
Emilyko is filled with loyalty towards the Shadow Family by
drinking the special coffee. Kate is shocked at her behavior,
and manages to relieve the brainwashing using information
from the notebook in Emilyko's room. Then Kate grabs the
exhausted Emilyko's hand and confides all her secrets to her.
Emilyko is abducted.
Kate confers with John and the others, and with an idea of
who the culprit is, they decide to venture to The Great
Grandfather's Wing. With the cooperation of everyone who
overcame the Debut, they set foot into the hallway
of renown.
Emilyko is abducted.
Kate confers with John and the others, and with an idea of
who the culprit is, they decide to venture to The Great
Grandfather's Wing. With the cooperation of everyone who
overcame the Debut, they set foot into the hallway
of renown.
[KATE] Next episode,
"To Lord Grandfather's Wing."
Next Episode
To The Great Grandfather's Wing