[KEITA]
Tendo.
Would you like to
go out with me?
[KAREN]
Uh-huh! I would love to!
See? That's the guy.
How the hell did he
pull it off, though?
Okay. I know I shouldn't
say this, but...
She's light-years outta
that nerd's league.
[KEITA]
Looks like they disconnected.
So much for a good match.
Damn, I'm super jealous
of that dude.
I wish I had a hot
blonde girlfriend
who was crazy about me.
Quiet down, you idiots,
he's gonna hear us!
[sighs]
[KEITA]
Uehara.
I've decided that I need
to stop demolishing
my classmates' expectations.
Uh-huh. I have no idea
what you're talking about,
but I'm glad your
reign of terror or
whatever is finally
coming to an end.
Just in time, too.
You're getting a crazy
amount of attention.
The horror.
Don't act like an
innocent bystander.
Last time I checked,
this was partially your fault.
Well, that's a fair point.
Guess I gotta own it.
But how was I supposed to
know you were gonna skip
the friends thing and go
straight for the jugular?
That moment was pretty god-tier.
Yeah. Kinda wild, huh?
[KEITA] Even though
Tendo said yes to me.
What if it was all just a ruse
to get closer with Uehara?
It's possible.
I wish I could borrow
some of your luck.
I don't even know what
I'm supposed to say
to Aguri after all that.
Huh? Can't you just
talk like normal?
How are we supposed
to do that, huh?
The guy Aguri likes
is with Tendo now.
[KEITA] Hold on. The guy she
likes is with Tendo now?
Don't make me spell it out!
See ya.
[TEACHER 2A]
Good morning. Take your seats.
[KEITA] The guy Aguri
likes is with Tendo.
But Aguri doesn't like any guys,
except...
[KEITA screams] That means
Uehara is cheating on her!
And that's why he doesn't
know what to say!
He's caught in a web
of his own lies!
[KEITA sighs]
I get it now.
It's easier for him to pursue
his secret romance at school
if everyone thinks Tendo's
going out with me.
Maybe she'll let me take back
the whole "wanna go out?"
thing I sprung on her.
I mean, it was a mistake anyway.
Sorry! I should've looked
where I was go--!
[BOTH gasp]
[sputters]
[clears throat]
What's the matter?
Say something.
You're even paler than
usual right now.
Uh! I'd... love to stay
and chat with you,
but I have to take care of
a thing somewhere else!
I'll see ya later! Good-bye!
Huh? Uh, bye.
[KEITA whimpers]
[KEITA]
Sorry, Tendo. That was lame.
[sighs]
Huh?
Hey, you! Twelve o'clock!
Whatcha want, moe -hater?
It's about what happened
yesterday! Okay.
We all know Tendo said yes,
but you know why she
said yes, don'tcha?
Uh. I can hazard a guess.
It's probably some kind of
mission of mercy on her part.
Well, as long as you're aware!
I gotta say, though, if that
were a quick-time event,
you rocked it!
[KEITA]
Yeah.
I guess I had a few
lucky button-presses.
The moment she said yes,
you cast a major debuff
on that she-devil
who was hanging on you
for all the wrong reasons.
Uh. "She-devil"?
Uh! Don't mind me!
Just thinking aloud!
We might be enemies,
but that doesn't mean
I wanna see you suffer
in matters of the heart.
What...?
You're gonna make me
spell it out, then? Fine!
Aguri might be nice
in most ways,
but she was never really
your girlfriend, 'kay?
It's time to face the truth.
Clearly.
She can't be my girlfriend
if we never went out.
This is awesome!
You don't seem
like you're pining for
what you used to have at all!
I didn't have anything,
so why would I be
pining for it, Einstein?
Now you're talking!
Out with the old and
in with the new, right?
You're adjusting to this
change like a real pro!
Okay.
[bell rings]
[AGURI] What, are the stickers
not clear enough?
Uh...
[AGURI growls]
[KEITA]
Can you ever forgive me?!
[AGURI giggles] Aw, come on,
don't freak out on me.
I'm 20% just kidding!
I don't feel so hot about
80% not kidding!
[sighs] Well, whaddya
want from me?
Ever since I got proof
that Tasuku's been
sneaking around on me
with other girls,
the whole world
just seems kinda blah.
[KEITA] Okay, but don't you
think maybe it's a stretch
to assume that he's cheating on
you, just because he looked at
you funny during my big
moment with Tendo?
Then why'd he make that
weird face at me, huh?!
I'm his cute little girlfriend!
There's no need to look
panicked, but he did!
[KEITA]
Uh, good point.
Hanging around with you has
given me nothing but bad luck.
No offense, but my life is
turning into a real suck-fest.
Hey, don't say it like that.
Makes it sound like I'm
jinxed or something.
Well, you're definitely not a
rabbit's foot, that's for sure.
Hoshinomori and Tendo both
met Tasuku because of you!
But, Uehara didn't seem to care
if he hung out with Tendo
so long as I got to.
Then again, he could've
used me as his cardboard box
to sneak in for the
kill, whatta snake.
I don't think he'd make
you be his camouflage.
When it comes to your
friendship, you guys're solid!
Yeah!
Maybe I'm that
expendable team member
you only swap into the
party for side-missions.
[growls] C'mon!
Stop being so negative!
It's annoying!
So, what're you going to
do about this Tendo thing,
now that it's way
more complicated?
Uh! It's hard to say.
Do you think
I should break up with her,
since I didn't mean to ask?
Don't ask me.
It's your life, Amano.
[KEITA]
Yeah. I guess you're right.
What's important is
how you feel,
and nobody else can
figure out that stuff.
Huh?
I'm serious. Look.
Whether you wanna be in this
relationship or you wanna bail,
you need to make up
your own mind about it.
Uh--
I'm sorry. You're right,
I just need to sack up and
face this problem head on.
Sounds good. Attaboy.
Gross! What the heck did I get?!
[KEITA]
Wait, you liked it fine before!
I honestly didn't notice
the flavor until just now!
Guess my tongue had
Tasuku on the brain!
[BOTH laugh]
See ya later!
[KAREN] Amano got in touch with
me out of the blue this morning.
Why did he want to
meet me up on the roof?
What if he wants to talk about
the state of our relationship?
Stop it, Karen.
Try to stay calm.
This is terrible!
I don't want him to
see me freaking out!
What if Amano didn't even
mean to ask me out
in front of everyone
in the first place?
It kills me to think of it,
but that would explain a lot,
I guess. I mean, really.
How come he just popped
the question
like that without any warning?
I'm scared to see him.
What if he just wants
to break up?
[KEITA]
Hey, thanks so much for coming!
Sorry it's so last-minute!
[KEITA]
Do you, um...
Do you hate me, Tendo?
If you do, just say so, and
I won't bug you anymore.
No, of course not!
If that's true, then why
won't you look at me?
I don't get it.
You know why!
And I know why we're
meeting up here!
Huh?
You brought me out on the roof
so you could break up
with me in peace and quiet,
isn't that right?
Uh!
It's fine. I get it.
You don't need to sugar-coat
the harsh truth of the
matter for my sake.
That face you made when I saw
you in the hall spoke volumes.
No, you just startled me.
Whatever! You don't have
to twist yourself in knots
to try and make me feel better!
You wanna take it back when
you asked me out, right?
Well, don't worry.
I meant it when I said yes,
but I definitely
got caught up in the heat
of the moment, too.
[KAREN] No. Why am I
acting all closed off again?
[KEITA]
I think, most of all,
I'm relieved, you know?
[KAREN]
About what?
I mean, you don't seem
to hate me or anything,
and everything beyond that
is kind of a bonus round.
Of course I don't.
How dumb would you have
to be to think I do?
Oh. Hey. Well, that's a plus.
And I hope you still
feel that way,
but first I have to get
this off my chest.
[KAREN]
Here it comes...
If it's not too much
of an imposition,
would you please go out on
a date with me, Tendo?
[gasps]
I know you're busy, but we can
do it whenever works for you.
And, I'm sure I'll be fine with
any place you'd like to go.
Hold on. What the heck
is happening right now?
I asked you on a date, which
seemed to prompt karate-hands.
No, I heard you say all
the words. It's just...
Is it that weird?
I mean, we are
boyfriend-girlfriend now.
[KAREN grunts]
Don't get me wrong! I'm not
saying this is going to be
the easiest relationship
in the world!
And we're not exactly equals
when it comes to the high school
food-chain thing, you know?
Honestly? A guy like me could
never hold a candle to Uehara.
He's ranked, and I'm still
working through the tutorial.
[KAREN]
Uh...
So what if I suck?
As a gamer, I think it's wrong
to quit out of a match!
If you're gonna play,
you play to win!
[KAREN gasps]
Are you all right, Tendo?
Sure! I mean, I guess I can.
A date would be pretty nice.
Like you said, we are
boyfriend and girlfriend now,
so this sort of development
is par for the course!
It's out of our control!
This is probably way late,
but even though I'm
a total noob at this,
I really look forward to
whatever time we get to
spend together as a couple.
I promise you that.
[KAREN] Uh, thanks.
That's very polite of you.
I'm looking forward
to it myself.
Ooh! But if you have any plans
of pulling a speed-run,
think again!
Don't you go anticipating
any double-XP weekends!
Okay?
You kind of lost me there, but,
right! No bonus modifiers!
Good! Don't you forget it.
Now, if that's all
you had to say,
you are dismissed
for the afternoon!
Yes, sir! Have a safe
walk home, Admiral Tendo!
You as well!
[KAREN] Wait! Why are we
saluting each other?
I'm his girlfriend,
not his ranking officer!
But, it's not like I can just
let down my guard, right?
I have to keep him
at arm's length
for the sake of my own sanity!
If he gets any closer to me,
I'm gonna lose my mind!
[KEITA]
Behold!
The place where normies go when
they wanna pretend to be gamers!
Around 1.
All right then.
Shall we give it a go?
Yes! Good idea!
[KAREN] It looks like arcade
games are on the first floor.
That's a lucky break for the
likes of us, but maybe we should
leave those for later on!
Let's see here.
Maybe we should
start out with the...
Aw, geez. I dunno.
This place is six stories tall!
Mm. Mm?
How about we just wander
around for a little bit?
We can do whatever
looks like fun. Right?
Okay.
[KEITA groans]
Oh, my gosh!
This place is amazing,
isn't it?!
[KEITA] It... It's definitely
something else.
It's kinda weird, though.
All of this sporty stuff
feels way more fun here
than back in PE class.
Right? Maybe it's
because we want to.
Having a coach bark at
you to do something
sort of kills the appeal.
I'm sure that's part
of the reason why,
but there's more to it.
Huh?
Uh! So! What do you
wanna try out next?
[KEITA]
Lemme check the map.
Okay, then. It looks like
there are a couple more
sports attractions
we haven't hit yet.
[gasps]
Nope! My bad!
The only thing left
to do is the arcade!
Isn't there a big pool
area under your hand?
Yeah. I must've missed
that part somehow.
Why don't we check it out?
Just give it a try
and see what we think?
I'm sure they rent swimsuits,
so we're covered.
Uh?!
Oh, I get it.
You're avoiding the pool
so you don't have to face the
sight of me in a bikini, huh?
Uh-- No. I...
It's not that I don't want
to see you in one, okay?!
[KAREN]
Chill out, Amano. I was kidding.
Uh.
Wait! I do wanna see you in
a bikini, but I shouldn't!
Nobody should! Does "Helen
of Troy" ring any bells?!
Women have doomed
humanity before! Huh?
Hey, it's all right.
If you don't wanna go to the
pool on our date, that's fine.
[KEITA] The year is 20XX,
and humanity is doomed.
[KAREN]
Sorry that took so long!
Anyway. I hope the
suit looks okay.
[KEITA screams]
I knew she'd be cute,
but I didn't expect her
to one-shot me!
Thank you for this boon!
That's kind of a
weird thing to say
when a girl asks you how
she looks in a swimsuit.
You look amazing in it,
but I didn't want to
cheapen the moment with
generic compliments!
[KAREN] Give me one generic
compliment, at least!
I even put this dumb
flower in my hair!
"Lookin' good, champ!"
Wow, good job.
[COUPLE laughing]
Stop! You're such a meanie!
I'm serious!
That looks pretty fun.
Do you wanna give it a try?
Huh?
But if we do, we need to
establish some ground rules
before the splashing can begin.
[KEITA]
Rules? Like what?
How about this?
The game is turn-based,
with the attacker getting
to throw water once per
round of the encounter!
Rounds are 10 seconds
or till an attack,
whichever comes first!
Whoever gets the other person's
hair wet is the champion!
[KEITA] Tendo, you've
got control issues.
Ready for a good soaking?
[KEITA] Yeah! Come at me
with all you've got!
[KAREN]
Curses!
[KEITA] Now it's my turn!
I'll wait a moment,
to lull her into a false
sense of complacency!
Go!
No! Why did I take the bait?!
[yells]
[KEITA]
Counterattack!
I've lost.
[laughs] I am the champion!
[GIRLFRIEND 7A]
I'm gonna get you, ya big cutie!
Take that!
Man, that was adorable!
I'm gonna get you! I'm...
Yeah, maybe you and I
should head over to
the arcade games already.
I just threw up in
my mouth a little.
[BOTH gasp]
[GUY 7A] If you're flying solo,
you can hang with us!
[gasps]
[gasps] Keita!
[CHIAKI whimpers]
Hey, you wanna give me
that arm back, kelp-head?
Just shut up for two seconds!
Look, pretend we're a
couple for a minute!
They'll lose interest if
they think I'm spoken for.
Aw, screw it.
She's here with a guy.
[BOTH sigh]
[KAREN laughs]
Ah! What are you doing?!
Tendo's right there!
Huh? Yeah, I noticed
her right away.
Hey, Tendo. It's nice
to see you again.
Yeah! A pleasure!
I don't wanna be a jerk about
it, but I happen to be here
with the girl whose boyfriend
I technically am right now!
Wait, are you trying to say
that you're on a date?
I figured that out when I saw
you two together, genius!
If you know we're on a date,
then why are you taking
my elbow to second base?!
I guess that you're right.
I shouldn't get in the way.
Even if your relationship
is just a total act
that she's putting on
to help you out.
Who says it's a total act?
--Huh?
Whenever you two are done!
[BOTH squeal]
[CHIAKI]
I am sorry to intrude, though.
I never meant to be
a third wheel.
It's not a big deal.
But, what are you doing
here all by yourself?
Oh, that's right!
My little sister wanted
to come here today
so she invited me along,
but we got separated
and now I have no idea
where she could be.
I'm pretty worried about her.
Hey Hoshinomori, we'd be happy
to help you look for her.
She's probably looking
for you, too,
so I bet we'll find
her in a snap!
[gasps] That would be great,
if you both don't mind.
It's not like I've got
anywhere else to be, right?
Count me in.
Thanks so much.
[KAREN] Thanks, but us girls can
handle the search-and-rescue.
[KEITA, CHIAKI]
Huh?
[KAREN] Amano doesn't need
to help us look for your sister,
so you can put a cork in
all that blushy gratitude.
He's gonna wait by himself
way over by the video
games, isn't he?
Uh, copy that, sir!
Wait by the games! Aye-aye!
Very good, soldier.
Better get marching, Amano!
Company dismissed!
Yes! Godspeed, sir!
You're a lot more
formal with each other
than I woulda thought.
[KAREN]
Thanks for waiting!
I hope that you're ready
for the main event!
[KEITA] So, why is Chiaki
still hanging around?
Oh, wow!
As it turned out, we
couldn't find my sister
because she'd gone home.
Wait, why are we
talking about that?!
I can see it in your face!
You don't have the
foggiest idea why Tendo
bothered to go on a date
with you today, do you?
Huh?
Honestly, Keita!
Is this so-called date doing
anything for you at all?
It's too late for you,
but you could still do
something nice for her,
if you'd use your
brain for once.
I don't get it.
What're you trying to say?
[laughs] I'm handing you a
golden opportunity here, dummy,
check it out! The chance to
make your girlfriend happy
with some head-to-head
game competition!
Why does it feel like you're
looking for an excuse
to play something?
Whaddya mean? I would never...
[KAREN]
Did you say, "competition"?
That sounds like a great idea!
[KEITA]
Uh...
This game is the sort where
there's no clear winner
until the very last lap is run!
Even though I've only
ever played this at home,
you're going down, Keita!
[KEITA] Both of you
are gonna rue the day
you picked this for our
competition! And go!
Just givin' you guys
a lead start!
Heh! That's what you get
for picking a tricky car
you don't know how to handle!
[KEITA growls]
[KAREN] You can bounce back,
so don't give up!
Uh, right!
Awesome driving!
Way to finesse that curve!
Eat my dust!
Amano's not bad, either!
The controls are definitely
coming easier to me now!
[CHILDREN]
No way, you got Bomb Roulette!
Heh. Yeah, nice
knowin' you, buddy!
You just landed the item
that has a 50/50 chance
of blowing up you,
or every racer except you!
Using it on this course
can be a real gamble!
You're gonna regret
giving me that info!
I can see the finish line!
Victory is mine!
[KEITA]
Time for some roulette!
[KEITA grumbles]
[sighs]
[KAREN stifles laughter]
[KAREN laughs]
[KEITA]
Are you okay?
[laughs]
[KEITA]
Huh?
I don't mean to laugh in your
face, but the way you lost
at the finish line was
so hilarious! I'm sorry.
No, that's okay. I'm just
glad you're not mad
at me for pulling
that stunt at the end.
Why would I be?
Uh...!
It's just a hunch, but
you didn't use that item
at the end of the race because
you were invested in
beating us, am I right?
Sorry I didn't take the
competition more seriously.
[KAREN]
You did the right thing.
'Cause whether you won or lost,
we all had a lot of fun,
thanks to that.
Heh.
[KAREN]
You make gaming fun.
I like that.
Thank you.
And I like the way you never
go easy on me, Tendo.
How you challenge me.
[KAREN]
Still not very good
at the generic
compliments, are you?
You could've played it
safe on the turns
and handed me the
win back there, but,
I wouldn't have enjoyed the
victory unless I earned it.
That's me.
Too stubborn not to face every
challenge with all I've got.
You're not wrong.
But it's precisely those
qualities that make you so
special and unique. I mean that.
[KAREN gasps]
[KEITA]
By the way, Tendo, are you
playing that Fire Tactics
title that just came out?
Well, of course!
How could I not?
You know, I've been meaning
to ask how you like it so far!
Are you playing
casual or classic?
I'm classic all the way!
[KEITA laughs]
Saw that coming.