[beeping]
[KAREN] For Otobuki High
School student Karen Tendo,
it's never too early to
get up and greet the day!
[laughs]
Another beautiful
morning out there!
[KAREN]
As soon as she's awake,
she begins her day
with a nice, brisk jog.
For girls like Karen Tendo,
mornings are a precious time
for self-improvement.
[WOMAN 4A]
Good morning!
Good morning to you, too!
[MAN 4A]
Show that trail who's boss!
Right back atcha, sir!
[KAREN] And so I, Karen Tendo,
begin another day of promise
and possibility by putting
my very best foot forward!
After I've worked out my body,
it's time to work out my mind.
The early-morning quiet is
the perfect time to get some
studying done, especially
for today's busy student.
[KAREN] A light breakfast,
and then I'm almost ready
to head out the door.
People don't know this about me,
but I don't really put
too much extra effort
into my appearance.
How someone looks
shouldn't matter.
It's your personality and your
heart that make you special.
Right!
[KAREN]
When I get to school,
the first thing I do is catch
up with all of my friends.
Karen! How ya doin'?
Good morning!
Great, and you?
[KAREN] My approach is to
give each of life's moments
my full attention, and give
100% to whatever I do.
I hang out with friends
while we're on break,
but that's not all.
Hey, wait! Please let me
help you with that.
[KAREN] I also lend the
faculty a helping hand!
You're such a
responsible student!
[KAREN]
I don't have an ulterior motive.
In my opinion, you should help
out whenever you're able.
And with that, it's time for the
least favorite part of my day.
Heartbreak.
[REJECTED BRO 4A] Please say
that you'll go out with me!
[KAREN] I hate doing it, but if
someone's going to fall for me,
the least I can do is turn
them down face-to-face
and be clear about it.
I'm sorry.
[KAREN]
And I am.
My heart aches with
every rejection.
I don't like having
to hurt people.
After class, I head
to the game club.
Of which I'm secretly a
member and president.
We're small, but we're all
committed to honing our skills
until we're the very best
at what we play.
Some afternoons,
no one says anything.
The air is filled with
tension and resolve,
and I absolutely love it!
[KAREN]
When I get home,
I review the day's lessons,
and then I play a bit more
to make sure I'm up-to-date
on the other games out there.
Last but not least, I try and
get a full night's rest.
Good night, everyone.
[KAREN] Thus ends another
magnificent day in the life
of Karen Tendo, and tomorrow
will be even better!
[beeping]
[KAREN] For Otobuki High School
student Karen Tendo,
it's never too early to
get up and greet the day!
[gasps] Whoa, what the heck?
Why was I having a dream about
Keita Amano, of all people?!
An' why was it such a sexy one?!
[KAREN groaning]
[beeping continues]
[gasps] I forgot to
do my homework!
[KAREN] The early-morning quiet
is the perfect time to get some
studying done, especially
for today's busy student.
[screams] Why did I
sleep in so late?!
[KAREN]
A light breakfast.
Ah! Thanks for the grub!
[KAREN] And then, I'm almost
ready to head out the door.
People don't know this about me,
but I don't really put
too much extra effort
into my appearance.
How someone looks
shouldn't matter.
It's your personality and your
heart that make you special.
[KAREN] Ahh! I'm running
late! I gotta go!
[KAREN'S MOTHER]
Karen! Is that really
what you're wearing to school?
[crash]
[KAREN]
When I get to school,
the first thing I do is catch
up with all of my friends.
[gasps] Uh...
You okay?
Yeah, never better.
[KAREN]
My approach is to...
[gasps] Avalanche!
[STUDENT 4A]
Are you sure you're okay?
[KAREN laughs]
Totally. I'm awesome!
[gasping]
[KAREN] ...is to give each of
life's moments my full
attention, and give
100% to whatever I do.
I hang out with friends
while we're on break,
but that's not all.
I also lend the faculty
a helping hand!
...but I'm actually tryin'
to take that stuff
to the Chemistry classroom.
Yeah, I got it! Chemistry class!
But, we're actually getting
further away from it.
Don't be such a worrywart!
I'll get there!
Via Class F!
[LAB TEACHER 4A]
Huh?! That makes no sense.
[KAREN]
I don't have an ulterior motive.
In my opinion, you should help
out whenever you're able.
[HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS]
Uh...?
[KAREN]
Why isn't he here?
He should be at that desk by the
window, playing on his phone!
Uh, whatcha doin'?
[KAREN gasps]
[KEITA] How come you just keep
walking back and forth?
[KAREN]
And with that,
it's time for the least
favorite part of my day.
Heartbreak.
No. That's got nothing
to do with it.
Honestly, we don't know each
other very well, and I--
[REJECTED BRO 4A]
Are you into someone else?!
[gasps] Someone else?!
You think I'm interested
in some other guy?
No! No! That's
grade-A crazy-talk!
There's no one in this
school I wanna go out with!
I wanna go out with...
Uh! Whoa! Forget all that!
I'm definitely not
thinking about
wanting to go out with anyone!
[REJECTED BRO 4A]
Uh, can we maybe
bring it back to my
love-confession?
No. Short version,
it ain't gonna happen.
Wait! That came out wrong!
Aw, man. I didn't mean
to rip his heart out.
[KAREN] After class,
I head to the game club.
Of which I'm secretly a
member and president.
We're small, but we're all
committed to honing our skills
until we're the very
best at what we play.
Some afternoons,
no one says anything.
The air is filled with
tension and resolve,
and I absolutely love it!
Are you okay? You seem
kinda out of it today.
What's wrong?
Ah, I guess I'm a little
preoccupied lately.
My brain keeps jumping around
to these unrelated thoughts.
Huh. Like what?
Let me think...
Like the first time I talked to
Amano and he dropped those games
and I helped him
pick 'em all up.
Or the time I got him
to visit the club room!
Remember? That was fun!
Or the time he turned me down.
Or how he totally caught me
stalking his classroom today.
And especially how he defended
me and the game club
when he yelled at Uehara!
That one's definitely
part of the highlight reel!
Do ya feel me?
[laughs]
Suck it up.
'Cause your gaming skills
are in a tailspin.
What?!
[GAKUTO] You know what.
You're playin' like a scrub.
[yelps] Fatality!
Yeah. You're the president.
You gotta keep it legit.
[KAREN] They're so right.
I'm Karen Tendo, dammit.
Game club president!
It's time to forget about Amano,
and give video games my all!
Maybe he'll have
a change of heart,
and show up to
the club tomorrow.
Uh! Why'm I still
thinking about Amano?!
But, it's not like the club
needs him to be competitive.
Looking back, I don't even
know why I wanted to get him.
Honestly, I couldn't
care less if he joined!
But! If he came
around and wanted
to join the club after all,
I guess that would be okay.
Yeah. Why not?
And naturally, he'd need
someone to show him the ropes,
and who better than
little ol' me?
[KAREN laughing]
[KAREN] Thus ends another day
in the life of Karen Tendo.
I'm not sure if it's
magnificent anymore,
but it's definitely something.
♪♪♪
[PUYO SCORE GIRL]
Score! Great job!
[KAREN]
There! I gotcha back!
Not bad at all!
By the way, did you
hear anything more?
Hear anything?
What's going on with
Hoshinomori and Amano
[PUYO SCORE VOICE]
Score! Great job! Awesome!
Tendo? Is your
controller working?
Snap out of it!
[PUYO CREATURE]
Winner!
[KAREN]
The others called it.
I am getting worse at gaming.
[KAREN]
I look so dead.
I know why I'm playing
so bad lately.
[KAREN]
Yeah. There's no doubt about it.
Ever since the day
when Amano told me
that having fun was the most
important part of gaming to him,
playing to win just hasn't
held the same appeal.
It's... different now.
What the heck?!
I can't believe I let him get
into my heart like this!
[gasps] Head!
"Into my head like this"--
that's what I mean to say!
I definitely didn't
mean "heart"!
[KEITA]
Tendo?
Uh! What're you doing here?!
Who, me? Nothin' much.
I mean, hello.
[clears throat]
Well, it's a heck
of a coincidence.
Having a nice day?
[KAREN] Nailed it!
There's the ol' Tendo poise!
Yeah, I guess.
My mom yelled at me for playing
video games all morning long.
So, I thought I'd go
outside, y'know?
[KAREN] It's not like fresh
air is gonna kill you.
Since we're both here,
wanna go for a walk with me?
Huh? Like together?
Ah! I don't think that's
a very good idea, Tendo!
You and me, together,
on a Saturday?
Nothing good can come of it!
How about we don't...
What's so bad about it?
[KAREN] He's going to
shoot me down again.
No! This time,
I'm not gonna let him!
What's the matter?
It's not like you hate me or
something. Right, Amano?
No, of course not!
I think you're awesome!
[gasps]
Uh! It's just...
I don't wanna start any
more rumors, you know?
Like, that would be bad.
Oh, rumors like what? [yelps]
Oh, your face!
Hey! Are you all right?
Of course! Yeah!
Why do you ask? Nothing
to see here! Ha, ha!
Are you sure?
Uh. Anyway! I should
be heading off now!
See you at school, I guess!
Huh? Hey!
Can't just run off like that!
Uh... Huh? Something wrong?
I... I was only suggesting
that we could go on a walk.
It wouldn't be a date.
Anyway, it's going
to happen, okay?
[KEITA]
Really?
So, I don't get a choice
in the matter?
I have made the decision
for both of us!
But, I don't even know
where we're going!
Figures.
What does?
I told you this isn't a date.
And even if it were a date,
I'd still probably take
you to a game store.
No, I... I just didn't think
we'd be going where
you and I first met.
Check it out! Golden Memories !
Ooh! I've been looking
for this one!
[KAREN] You're already having
more fun than I am.
[KAREN gasping]
[KEITA]
Uh? Everything okay?
[gasps] Oh! Yeah!
Wonderful! I remember you
checking that game out before.
Ah! Crap! No!
It's not 'cause of the
wardrobe malfunctions
and the jiggle-physics,
I swear!
It's on sale!
You don't have to explain.
You're a boy, after all.
[KEITA] Why are you talking to
me like a mom who just found
her son's porn magazines?
I'm not gonna buy it!
Aw. Don't you want it?
[KEITA]
I am so confused right now.
Jiggle-physics, huh?
[sighs]
[KEITA] Where next on our
totally platonic walk?
[KAREN] Well, if the game
store was stop number one,
then number two is
obviously the arcade.
Obviously. Yeah. Good.
Wait a sec.
I don't think I knew you
ever went to the arcade.
It's only on the days when
the club doesn't get together
after school. What about you?
Arcade gaming always
used to intimidate me.
But then I gave it a shot
with someone, y'know?
And it wasn't so awful!
Really, it was a ton of fun!
[CHIAKI laughing]
[KAREN] When you say you gave
it a shot with someone...
[KEITA]
Wow. We made good time.
[KAREN]
Oh, look!
It's definitely the arcade! Yup!
[KAREN] He's-- He's
talking about Uehara.
Not about Hoshinomori, right?
He can't be! [groans]
Didja get a headache?
No! I just can't believe
you're the type a guy
who would go to an
arcade with some girl,
even if it only
happened in my mind.
I'm here 'cause you invited me!
[gasping]
[KEITA] Can I reload the whole
part of this encounter?
[KAREN]
Come on! Adventure awaits!
Let's do this!
[KEITA sighs]
[KAREN] If I can trounce him at
something here, maybe it'll
finally snap me out of this
slump I've been in lately.
[KEITA]
Mm?
Everything good?
Uh, yeah!
I wasn't expecting you to
bypass the crane games.
I know that a lot of people
go for this kind of stuff.
Uh-huh. They are popular,
but they've never really
held much appeal for--
[KAREN] Wait!
"People go for this stuff"?
What people?! Girl people?!
[BOTH laughing]
[KEITA]
Look, they match!
[CHIAKI]
Just like us!
[screams]
[grunting]
[KEITA]
When you're done with that,
do you wanna give
the token games a try?
See? They're giving out
triple the tokens today.
Lucky us, huh?
[KAREN]
Uh. Sure.
I'll get us ready.
I think 500 yen
should be enough.
Wait! Amano!
[KEITA laughs]
Hey, Tendo.
How come you're staring at me
like you just hit a boss fight
and you haven't saved
your game in forever?
This coming from the guy
who didn't check if I wanted
to play token games before
getting a bajillion of 'em!
Huh?
[KAREN] I wanted to beat
you at actual arcade games,
but whatever.
This'll have to do.
All right!
You and me, buddy!
Uh...
I didn't want to do this, but
you leave me with no choice!
Hey, if token games aren't
your thing, we can skip it.
No chance!
Right!
Okay, then. You picked
the weapon for our battle.
Of course, token games
rely solely on chance.
And that means either of
us could win this thing.
Why are you making it sound like
I'd lose if it were
based on skill?
[KAREN]
This is a battle for my life!
For my very reawakening
as a gamer!
I'm going to defeat you
and reclaim my lost mojo!
What are you talking about?!
Aren't we just playing
the token games for fun?
Yeah. Technically speaking.
Uh, girls are never
gonna like you
if you half-ass your
way through life!
I don't understand why you're
such a grumpy pants today.
Do ya feel lucky, punk?
Whoever has more tokens
in half an hour wins!
[KEITA]
O... kay.
All right! Let the
tokening begin!
[KAREN]
I'm gonna beat Amano like a drum
and kiss my gaming
slump goodbye!
[KAREN]
Pusher games are consistent.
They're always a safe bet.
Yeah, but the best seats
have already been taken.
And they're not great
for making it rain
when you're under
the gun, time-wise.
Uh?! Why'd he pick the
seat with the lowest total?
What's up your sleeve, pal?
Ha! So that's how
you play these!
[KAREN]
He's a total noob at this!
Granted, that kinda threw me
off, but I gotta stay focused!
Today, I'm gonna nip my Amano
problem right in the bud!
Turns out you need luck and
skill to win at token games,
and I didn't have either one.
I had a blast, though,
and next time I'll do better.
[KAREN]
I won, right?
So how come I feel like grinding
my teeth down to the gumline?
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps] Tendo!
Mind if I bum this
token off of you?
Huh? Yeah, knock yourself out.
[KEITA laughs]
Awesome, thank you!
What are you doing?
We don't want your token
going to waste, right?
All of my hopes are
riding on it.
All of your hopes...?
Yeah. Of winning.
I'm still trying to beat you
at our token challenge.
--Uh?
--Huh?
♪♪♪
[RACE ANNOUNCER 4A]
And they're off!
Number 2 and Number 8...
You... wanna win?
Duh, you challenged me.
But, you said all that
didn't matter to you.
What does that even mean?
I don't get it.
[KAREN] Win or lose,
I thought you didn't care.
Playing is fun, but if somebody
throws down the gauntlet,
you bring it!
[screams]
[RACE ANNOUNCER 4A] They've
entered the final furlong,
folks! It all comes
down to this!
Go! Go!
[RACE ANNOUNCER 4A] They're
pulling away from the pack!
And there's the race!
Number 4 wins, with Number 6
in 2nd, and Number 2 in 3rd.
Number 5 comes in dead last...
[KEITA]
Oh, well. Uh. You okay?
[KAREN]
Let's review.
Way back when, I asked you to
join our club, you said no
because we focus on competition.
Yeah. I guess that's a
pretty good way to put it.
Okay.
But when you lost the race back
there, you were bummed.
And that's because you
were trying to defeat me,
down to your last token.
None of it adds up!
You really think so?
You've always made it seem
like you're just about gaming
for fun. So you can't care
about winning and losing, too.
That's silly.
When I play a game,
of course I want to win.
Everybody does!
No, it doesn't work like that!
Having fun while you play
and playing to win
are two totally opposite...
[KEITA] ...sides of the
same coin, right?
[gasps]
Like, come on.
Who plays a video game without
caring if they win or not?
If you ask me, that doesn't
sound like any fun at all.
[gasps]
Ew...
--[chiming]
--Uh?
[gasps]
Hey! Look at the
vending machine!
Four sevens! I won! [laughs]
Must be my lucky day!
Here. Take it.
We'll call it your trophy.
Thanks a lot.
Sometimes I sit down to play
and it's like I've never seen
a game in my life, I'm so bad.
But I wanna win,
so I give it 100%.
[KAREN] So, why don't
you join the game club?
[KEITA]
'Cause even at 100%,
I don't have what it takes
to come out on top.
[KAREN]
I see...
Hey, Amano.
When I play, I get super worked
up over winning and losing.
The whole club does.
Do you think we're dumb?
[KEITA]
What are you talking about?!
That isn't dumb
in the slightest.
[gasps]
[KEITA] To savor the wins and
shake your fist at the losses,
that's what being a
gamer's all about, Tendo!
[KAREN gasping]
That's why, even though
the members of the game club
are way more intense than I am
about being the best player,
I support you guys all the way!
I get it.
[KEITA]
And me?
I guess I'm just wishy-washy.
I don't stick with a title long
enough, so I never learn how to
master the game like you do.
Honestly, you...
Just when I think I've
got you all figured out.
Uh. Sorry about that.
[KAREN] I meant it as
a compliment, dummy.
[KAREN] Okay! Today's
walk is officially done!
See ya later, Amano!
Okay. But, why'd you
wrap it up so quickly?
[KAREN]
Well, if you must know...
...there's a game back at home
that I'm dying to play!
♪♪♪
Tendo. What the hell?
[KAREN groans]
You're worse! Like,
way worse than before!
What is this?! You were
finally getting good again,
but now you're playing
like a toddler
who's got the controller
in their mouth!
[KAREN] Every time
it starts getting fun,
my mind drifts to Amano's face,
and then I get all distracted!
[groans] It's his fault!
Everything is Amano's fault! Ah!