[AGURI giggles]
You're silly, Amano!
I never mentioned a wolf!
I thought Tasuku was being a
snake, but that's different!
[KEITA]
It's an idiom!
[TASUKU] Clearly she's
depressed as all hell.
I'm just gonna mind
my own business.
[KAREN]
Uehara. What's up?
You seem like you're
wound kinda tight today.
What's with that nervous look?
Hey, can you even
blame me for that?
I'm surprised, that's all.
You always used to strike me
as a pretty cool customer.
Usually, yeah.
But I know how intense you
can get outta nowhere,
so it puts me on edge.
I'm not that bad.
Even Amano seems
to be calming down
and having more fun when we
hang out together lately.
He does? Pretty weird, huh?
I bet it's Aguri's influence
rubbing off on him.
I get what you're saying
because I feel like
she's been acting
more grown up as well lately.
[BOTH sigh]
Do you think that's Amano's
influence rubbing off on her?
Probably.
The little guy does have a way
of getting into your head,
as much as I hate to admit it.
Oh. I know.
And when you get close
to someone like that...
...your true self might
start emerging as a result.
[TASUKU] I guess Aguri's one
step closer to adulthood
thanks to Amano
spending time with her.
[KAREN] And Amano's that
much more of a person
thanks to all those
afternoons spent with Aguri.
[BOTH] Could they be any
more perfect of a couple?!
[KAREN]
Just for the record,
I don't think those
two cinnamon rolls
are sneaking around behind our
backs or anything like that.
Yeah. I know.
[TASUKU] Neither of them would
ever be cool with cheating
on the person they're dating.
They're not wired for deception.
But still...
Here it is.
I don't know if he and
I have anything more
than what Aguri has
with him as a friend.
Maybe he's meant to be her
boyfriend instead of being mine.
[TASUKU]
Screw that.
I'm not giving up yet!
We can turn this thing around!
[gasps]
How so?
They might be cinnamon rolls,
but I bet you and me
can get up to some pretty
top-tier scheming if we try!
Huh? What are you talking about?
I gotta know more, Uehara!
[TASUKU]
Uh, you mean like right now?
But aren't we standing
in front of your house?
[KAREN] I don't care where
the hell I'm standing!
Tell me how we're gonna
save our relationships!
I wanna know more!
Uh. Okay, here's what I think.
Follow me here.
When your relationship status
gets all vague and junk,
what's the absolute
sure-fire method
to get stuff figured out again?
There is a way!
Well? Spit it out!
You show the world
that you're a couple.
And you show them!
[gasps]
Check it out.
If Aguri and Amano can
see how happy the other is
in their current relationship.
[KAREN]
Show them...
You okay?
Show them you're a couple!
[laughing]
[TASUKU]
How come I'm in cahoots
with Hoshinomori's
romantic rival?
[KAREN laughing]
[KEITA]
Huh?!
You wanna go on a double date?
[KAREN]
Yeah! What do you think?
Uh, what do you think about it?
You sound pretty hyped.
[KAREN] We can invite Uehara
and Aguri to come along,
and then we can go on some grand
adventure, just the four of us.
When you put it that way,
I guess it sounds like our gamer
meet-up at school, but...
But what?
Double dates are just so...
I mean, isn't it
weird to hang out
with another couple like that?
It almost feels
like we're trying
to prove something to the world.
[KAREN]
Prove something? As if!
Seriously.
We can try going out with
them if you really want to,
but I think I would be too
embarrassed to have any fun.
[KAREN] Well, I'm a
little nervous myself.
I've never done this sort
of thing before, so...
It does seem kinda
new-game-plus
compared to a typical
single-couple date.
That's exactly what it is!
What if the first boss
fight we encounter
wipes the floor with us
'cause we're underleveled?
It could happen!
[KAREN] I don't think we're
going to hit any boss fights.
Okay.
Just so I know where we're at,
are you absolutely opposed to
the idea of going out with them?
[KEITA]
I want to make Tendo happy.
That's what a good
boyfriend does.
But a man's gotta stick
to his guns, right?
[KAREN] I just thought
it would a fun idea...
Of course I'll go on a
double date with you, Tendo!
Four hearts are better than two!
[KAREN]
You mean it? Oh, thank you!
Okay, we'll meet
up at the station
this Sunday at ten
in the morning,
so don't stay up
late tomorrow night.
And don't worry about tickets
into the theme park.
My parents know somebody
who can get us some.
Just make sure to
bring enough money
for food and transportation,
and you'll be fine.
They have an evening
parade this time of year,
so we'll be getting
home pretty late.
Make sure you let
your parents know.
Maybe you should be
writing this down.
But it's all pretty
cut-and-dried, I think.
Sounds like
everything's covered.
Glad to hear it!
Then I'll see you bright
and early Sunday morning.
Sweet dreams tonight, Amano.
Uh, yeah, right.
Sweet dreams to you, too.
[beeping]
[BOTH] Spiel Kingdom,
in all its "whatever" glory!
[KAREN laughs]
[KAREN]
It's just like that crappy town
halfway through the game
that only has one quest!
[KEITA]
Yeah!
That town where the
vendors sell junk items
you stopped picking
up hours ago!
I don't get why they're
so hyped about this place,
it seems kinda lame.
Yeah.
Well, if you're a super fan of
the RPG they based this town on
and replicated here,
you'd be in gamer's heaven.
[BOTH]
Uh-huh!
[KAREN] Look at those gnomes!
They're just perfectly hideous!
[KEITA] I don't think I've ever
felt halfway through a game
more than I do in
this very moment!
Hey, uh, you play
games like this,
how come you aren't nerding out?
Because even for a
gamer like myself,
that level of spaz
gives me the creeps.
That's a relief.
I was worried that this place
was awesome and I didn't get it.
You're good. They're
nuts, that's all.
Wow!
This cheap, real-world look
is something to cherish!
These days, VR has
become all the rage.
Most folks would just program
something this blah!
Yeah, you said it!
Uh! Look at that statue!
It's dinged up, but not
too dinged up, y'know?
[AGURI]
Please, Tasuku!
We've only been
here five minutes
and I already wanna ditch 'em
the first chance we get!
Try to stay calm, Aguri.
For what it's worth,
I'm right there with ya.
[KEITA, KAREN] You guys aren't
having an argument, are you?
[TASUKU, AGURI] No, but if we
were, it'd be all your fault!
[KAREN]
So far, so good, right?
[TASUKU]
Yeah.
What's your take on
the situation, huh?
They're up there,
and we're back here.
I just don't know
about this double date.
How does Tasuku even
dream this stuff up? Crazy.
[KEITA]
Oh, gosh!
You don't really
know a restaurant
till you've seen
their breakfast menu!
You seem pretty upbeat
about this whole mess.
[KEITA]
Yeah, I am! Wanna know why?
Tell me why.
Because my girlfriend
and your boyfriend
decided for everybody that
we're all gonna go on a date
in front of each other!
There's nothing left for me
to get stressed out about!
It's game over, man! Game over!
[laughing]
It doesn't count
as being upbeat
if you're really just having
a nervous breakdown
and slapping a smiley
face on the front!
Uh, y'know, I like
this place and all,
but Tendo's really
excited to be here.
You don't think that
this double date...
...is camouflage...
[BOTH] ...to cover up the fact
that they're cheating on us!
[KAREN]
Uehara.
It's high time we begin
the charm offensive!
[TASUKU]
Copy that.
You an' me gotta
roll up our sleeves
and win some hearts here.
Whaddya think?
Maybe hold their hand first
to get that feels-train rollin'?
[KONOHA] Oh my gosh!
Fancy running into you guys!
[KEITA]
What the--? Is that Konoha?
What's going on, Konoha?
Tell me you didn't plan this!
[CHIAKI] Tomorrow, huh?
Isn't that sort of last-minute?
You don't have
weekend plans, anyway.
What the heck?
You know I spend
most of my off-time
getting my games up to snuff.
You shouldn't just assume
I've got nothing going on.
Think of it as practice
for when you go there
on a date with Amano.
[gasps] A date?
Who says that's even in
the realm of possibility?
Well, I've got
these free tickets,
but I don't wanna waste 'em.
But going sounds
like a lotta work.
I have so much to do on my game.
C'mon, are you going,
or wussing out?
Well, I'm not ready right now.
Plus, all things
considered, he's taken.
Keita has Tendo, so
what's the point anyway?
[KONOHA sighs]
Real-talk, Sis.
You gotta stop putting your
own feelings dead last.
Keita's feelings for online-you
are gonna fade away
while you're busy trying
to get your act together.
[grunts]
[giggles]
That's okay!
If you really wanna stay home,
maybe I'll see if Keita
wants to go with me!
Yeah, that's a great idea!
Have fun with your
code and stuff!
[CHIAKI]
I'll go.
Sorry, what was that?
[CHIAKI]
I'll go to the amusement park!
I'll be your plus-one!
Even though it's a pretend date,
wear your cutest clothes!
Good night!
My cutest clothes?
[KAREN] I don't care where
the hell I'm standing!
Tell me how we're gonna
save our relationships!
I wanna know more!
[KONOHA] I couldn't hear
what they were being
all sneaky about,
but there's no way
they're leaving Sis in the dust!
Not while I've
got these puppies!
I'm Chiaki's sister, Konoha!
[TASUKU]
Okay, so you're the sister.
[KONOHA]
Hey now, that is close enough!
I don't go for ugly older dudes!
[TASUKU]
Ugly older dudes?
[TASUKU groaning]
What are the odds we'd
all be here on the same day?
[KONOHA gasps]
Yeah, that's pretty
coincidental!
Wouldn't you agree, Sis?
You know what, though?
Isn't it a little rude to hold
an official gamers
meet up activity
without one of your most
important members present?
Just sayin'.
Hey, I'm sorry about that.
We didn't mean to make you
feel left out, I promise.
It's just that we-- We're
actually double dating, so...
Ah! So the four of you
came here on a double date!
I can't imagine doing
something so public myself.
How brave of you!
Um, what if we hung out
in one big group
so the two of you could
get to know each other?
[KAREN, KONOHA]
The hermit is giving us advice?
[KEITA]
K.O.!
[snickers]
[KONOHA] Why do they let
you spin 'em that fast?
Are you okay?
Yeah! Never better! I mean it!
Don't worry about me!
[laughing]
Let's do this next, guys!
Yeah. It's Spiel Kingdom's
most famous attraction.
The Kizuna Dungeon.
Whoa! They really
nailed the atmosphere!
[AGURI] I love it! Creepy stuff
like this is right up my alley!
Something wrong?
Oh! I'm fine!
Nothing to worry about!
Okay.
[TASUKU] C'mon, Tendo. You
can't throw in the towel yet!
[KAREN]
Yeah, you're right.
There's still time
to turn this around!
[KONOHA laughs]
Hurry up! The Kizuna
Dungeon awaits!
[VOICE A]
Lockie the Hero?
I wouldn't expect to find
you in a place like this!
Oh, wow. It's really
detailed, huh!
Yeah, they pulled out all
the stops for this one.
[VOICE A] The traps in here
might annoy you, but trust me.
Try not to get too
steamed about them!
[AGURI screams]
[VOICE A] Shocking what
you'll find stuck in a wall!
[KEITA wheezes]
[VOICE A] A bunch of the
Evil King's minions
are waiting somewhere up ahead!
[KAREN screams]
Tendo, are you okay?
Yeah, I am now.
[VOICE A]
The inky darkness awaits you!
Step forth with that
special someone,
and let the strength of
your bond carry the day!
Chiaki. Are you
sure you're okay?
Well, wanna give it a shot?
Yeah!
Then, I guess it's our turn.
Shall we, Amano?
[KAREN]
Amano?
[KONOHA]
Ah!
Yay! There we go!
Nice fresh air!
What's the big idea?
I was about to go
in there with Tendo!
Oh, I'm sorry!
You looked a little
green around the gills.
Yeah, thanks for that.
You're not looking so
good yourself, Chiaki.
Hey, what's the matter?
I'm fine, okay?
Stop worrying about me.
I'm just a little
dizzy. That's all.
She fainted!
[KONOHA]
Oh no, Sis!
I'm glad you're finally awake.
You wanna move your head?
My leg's asleep.
Oh. Sorry about that, Konoha.
I really am fine now.
Are you really okay?
What are you doing back there?!
Amano's actually the one who
carried you over here, Sis.
Uh! Like carried me carried me?
You're stronger than you look.
Though I guess you couldn't
be much weaker, huh?
[KEITA grumbles]
You still look pale,
so take it easy for a bit.
I'm pale all the time,
not just now!
[snickers]
[KONOHA]
Well, then!
I'm going to go buy us some
drinks! You two hang tight!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Oh, I'd be happy to get them.
[KONOHA] No chance, Amano!
You wait here with my sister.
Just in case she needs
carrying again, okay?
All right.
Stop staring at me!
It makes me uncomfortable!
Oh, sorry.
[CHIAKI sighs]
I--
[phone buzzing]
Hey. It's Tendo.
I should take this.
[KEITA]
Huh?
[CHIAKI gasps]
I'm sorry I grabbed your arm.
It's just, when I'm in
big places like this,
I get a kind of anxious
all by myself.
I'll stay.
But Tendo--
[KEITA]
She'll probably text.
I mean, she's pretty
diligent like that.
[phone buzzes]
See? There she is now.
She says they're waiting
for us over by the dungeon.
You should be with her.
[KEITA]
Don't you wanna sit down?
[KEITA] Spending the whole
day at a theme park like this
can be pretty overwhelming.
Between that and
all the walking,
it's no wonder you keeled over!
What made you two wanna come
here today, in particular?
I got dragged into it!
Konoha wanted me to scope
out this place for a date
she's pushing me to go on!
[KEITA]
Really?
Hold on! Who're you thinking
of going on a date with?
Why would you ask me that?
What difference does
it make who it is?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Can I ask you something?
I wanna know... what do you
think of Mono and Nobe?
Think of her, I guess.
To tell the truth,
I'm still getting used to
the fact they're Konoha.
But nothing's changed.
Not in any way that matters.
They're still really
important to me.
[CHIAKI]
More important than Tendo?
Hey, wait.
How come you're making it
sound like a competition?
[CHIAKI]
Forget it! I'm just being nosy!
I was trying to
make conversation.
Tendo means a lot to me.
I've always thought
that she was special.
Sometimes I suddenly
remember at random moments
that we're actually going out
and I just can't believe
how fortunate I am.
It's the same, though.
When I think about
Uehara and Aguri,
they're really important
to me, as well.
Just like you, Chiaki.
[KEITA] I was a loner with
zero friends until recently.
I would've never imagined
that I'd get to hang out
with you guys like
this, you know?
[KEITA chuckles]
And none of it would've happened
if Tendo hadn't taken the time
to say hello to me that
one day at the game store.
I just wish I could figure out
why she likes me so
much in the first place.
Honestly, we still seem
like a pretty odd couple.
Stop trying to sound
all humble, you butthead.
What the--? Who's
trying to be humble?
All I wanted to do
was explain myself!
[yelping]
[CHIAKI]
Konoha?
[KONOHA clears throat]
[KONOHA humming]
What about the drinks?
Why don't you walk all the way
over there and buy us some
if you're so damn thirsty?
What?!
We should get a move on.
I'm sure everyone else
is waiting for us.
[KONOHA]
Hm?
You go on. I think I'm
gonna call it a night.
Already, Sis?
[KEITA]
Are you still feeling woozy?
No, but I think you
should at least
get to spend what's left of
the day with your girlfriend.
[KONOHA]
Chiaki.
It's okay.
[KEITA]
You can't go home yet.
After all, you wouldn't
wanna miss the parade.
Come on!
Uh! Hey! Wait for me, you two!
[KEITA]
Sorry you had to wait!
Way to leave us hangin', Amano!
[AGURI]
Where the heck were you guys?!
[KEITA] We'd have been back
sooner, but Chiaki passed out.
What? I'm fine really!
I was a little lightheaded
earlier, that's all.
[KAREN]
Thank goodness!
[AGURI gasps]
[AGURI]
You guys, we've gotta hurry!
The parade is starting up!
It's time for that already?
Yeah, it's like the
highlight of coming here!
We can't miss it!
[AGURI]
Move those skinny legs, Amano!
[KAREN] Come on, Hoshinomori!
The parade awaits!
[KEITA] Look how many
people showed up for this!
[AGURI gasping]
[AGURI gasps]
Hey! What'cha doin'?
Why don't we go to the front
so we can see 'em better?
[AGURI]
Uh.
Oh! Okay!
[KAREN sighs]
[KAREN]
Huh?
Amano?
You wanna move up
to the front, too?
[KAREN]
Uh.
Well, duh!
But I'm only holding your hand
'cause I know for a fact you'll
get lost in the crowd otherwise!
So hold on tight!
'Kay, let's get moving, Tendo!
That's the spirit!
I'm sorry about today, Sis.
I may have gone
overboard a little bit.
Everything worked out fine.
[KONOHA]
Well, how'd it go?
[CHIAKI]
What do you mean?
Did he shoot you down?
No, he didn't "shoot me down."
Thanks for the
vote of confidence!
[KONOHA]
You didn't tell him, didja?!
[CHIAKI] The time wasn't
right. I'm being strategic!
I swear!
Though I didn't tell
him the truth today,
I promise someday I will
make Keita a slave
to my overwhelming charms
in the romance department!
Who're you?
Chiaki the Barbarian?
[BOTH laughing]
[CHIAKI] Let's go to the
front with the rest of 'em!
[KONOHA]
Sure! But don't faint, okay?
'Cause I can't lift you!
[CHIAKI] I won't!
I'm feeling great right now.
C'mon, Konoha! Onward!
[CROWD cheering]
Whoa! What's up?
You're the bestest, Tasuku.
No, you are.
I'm really glad that today
wasn't game over, after all.
It's so pretty.
Hey, Tendo! What do you
say we get even closer?
[KAREN]
Okay!
[KEITA screams]
Are you all right?