[AGURI]
So you want me to be part
of your gamer meet-up thing?
That's right.
But I don't really play games.
Wouldn't that be weird?
That doesn't matter to us.
As long as you have
a love for the genre.
Yeah. I'm pretty "whatever"
about 'em, you know?
As long as you love someone
who has a love for the genre!
Get it?
Awesome! Then I can
join the meet-up!
And I'm always looking
for more chances
for me and Tasuku
to hang out together.
But I don't wanna be
that annoying girlfriend
who never gives
her guy any space.
[grumbles]
Uh, not that it matters,
but I've invited Tendo
to join, as well.
[gasps]
So Tendo's gonna be there?
I don't care either
way, of course!
Tendo's always been a
gamer, so it makes sense.
Nothing weird about that at all!
I'm loving this dessert!
It is so good!
[KEITA]
How about seconds, then?
You mean it? Yay!
If you promise me you'll
come to the meet-up,
this is all yours.
Fine, then! I promise I'll go.
Now gimme that plate!
Well, if that's the case,
sounds like we've got a deal!
[KEITA]
Eat up, Aguri.
At least that torte will
never betray your affections.
I mean, Tasuku
did confess his love
to another girl
behind your back.
If you wanna double-down
on dessert, you do you!
[KEITA]
Okay.
I'm still confused by all this,
but congratulations, Chiaki.
The guy you have a crush on
told you that he likes you back.
You've gotta be on
cloud nine, right?
Hm? Why the long face?
Uh, I guess... I'm just shocked.
Yeah.
The fact I like a boy
and he likes me,
that's pretty
incredible, isn't it?
This is awesome.
As if!
I'd turn this guy down
without a second thought,
and you should, too!
Yeah, the two of you
may like each other,
but isn't he already spoken for
in the girlfriend department?
He'd better not come
sniffing after you, Sis.
I'll punch his cheating face!
[KEITA]
She's right!
If Chiaki and Uehara end up
together because of this,
how am I supposed to look poor
Aguri in the face again?
Okay!
Let's send this player to
the burn ward, you guys!
Um, I don't know if I can.
This is all kinda new to me.
I've never rejected
someone before.
[KEITA gasps]
We could get some
advice from a girl
who's rejected dozens of guys!
[KAREN]
Uh, hey, Amano! What's up?
Hey, Tendo.
I'm sorry to call
you up like this,
but I need to know how
to reject someone's
romantic advances on the double!
[KAREN]
What?
Rejecting someone is tough,
and I have no idea how to do it.
I could use some advice!
[KAREN] Uh, is-is this just
a hypothetical question,
or a real-life problem?
Real-life! It's
happening right now!
[KAREN]
No! I can't!
Wha--?!
Please, I beg of you!
I don't know who else
to turn to with this!
And if it's going to happen,
I could really use
your help, okay?
[KAREN]
If it's going to happen?
You blindside me
with this phone call,
and you're not sure either way?
I shouldn't have said if!
It's definitely going to happen,
but I'm hoping we
can do it right!
[KAREN] I can't believe you're
asking me to help! It's cruel!
Just because I turn people down
a lot, it doesn't mean that--
[KAREN crying]
What's going on?
Say something, Tendo!
Out of nowhere, it sounded like
you got majorly punched-out!
[KAREN] If by "majorly
punched-out" you mean
"took a brutal uppercut
in the final round,"
then basically, yeah!
[KEITA]
Huh?
Please, just hang in there!
I'm on my way over to you!
What?
Why would you bother
coming over to help me
if you were going to--?
I'd never let you suffer!
What guy wouldn't run to his
beloved girlfriend's rescue?
[KAREN]
Beloved?
[crash]
Are you still there?
[KAREN]
The Eagle has landed.
What does that even mean?
[KAREN] Sorry for freaking
out on you before.
I'm okay now.
No. I'm excellent!
I still don't get the thing
you said about the eagle!
[KAREN]
Amano?
Yeah? I'm here.
[KAREN]
I love you.
[click]
[beeping]
I don't think I'll ever know
how I got a girlfriend
who's so adorable.
[KONOHA] How's that supposed
to help my sister, huh?!
Sorry about that. Had a
bit of mission creep.
What about you? I'm sure you've
dealt with it before, right?
Dealt with what, loser?
Y'know, turning people down
when they confess
their feelings to you.
You're cute.
So I'm sure that sort of thing
happens to you all the time.
[gasps]
Well, when I turn them down,
I usually give 'em the ol'
"I'm flattered that you like me,
but I don't have time for
that stuff right now."
[KEITA laughs]
Yeah! "No time"!
Hentai games keep you busy--?
Whatever do you mean?
Hentai games keep you busy,
but they're not helpful now.
'Cause I just get freaky
with all the girls.
I've never turned any
of those nymphos down!
[KEITA laughing]
[KONOHA clears throat]
Well, when I tell
people I'm too busy,
I'm not exactly lying.
My student council president
duties eat up at lot of my time.
You're a different story.
Fair enough.
But I do spend a lot of time
working on my games,
so that's an excuse.
Oh yeah, right.
I forgot that you dabble
in freeware game design
a little bit too.
Like Nobe, like
sister! Oh, yeah!
Yes! The two of us just
love programming!
That's cool, but could you
maybe sit back down again?
It's embarrassing.
[sighs]
With Uehara liking you,
and all the other girls
who are involved in this whole
situation, I guess there's...
...there's only one
way to get this
whole thing straightened out.
Here's what we're gonna do!
We're gonna drag Tendo and Aguri
to the next gamers meet-up,
and we're not leaving that room
until all of us are
on the same page!
[KEITA]
Achievement unlocked!
[TASUKU]
Hey, Amano--
Everybody, thank you
for taking the time
to come to the meet up.
I appreciate you clearing
your schedules for this.
You're here because I need to
discuss something with you.
It's a topic of the
utmost importance.
Hey, Amano. Where're
you going with this?
[AGURI] I've never seen your
serious-business face before.
Whatever the meeting's about,
it's gotta be a bombshell.
It is. And it couldn't wait.
Not even one more day.
We need to talk about...
[KEITA]
To talk...
...about how as a group...
...none of you even
know how fast
I'm gonna buy Space
Ocean 5 tomorrow!
[TASUKU, KAREN, AGURI]
That's your big reveal?
What the heck?
I thought you were gonna talk
about the Uehara thing!
I'm sorry!
Seeing everyone staring at me
really stressed me out, okay?
So what are you
going on about?
Space Ocean doesn't
ring any bells.
Actually, it's an RPG.
Even more specifically,
it's the fifth installment
in my absolute favorite
game franchise.
I was gonna run over
to the game store
as soon as class lets out
tomorrow to buy the new one.
You're correct about 5
hitting the shelves tomorrow.
As a fellow fan, I'm
buying a copy myself.
You preordered, right?
Well, of course I did.
That's what I'd be saying
if this were any other Space
Ocean game coming out.
But I guess I forgot
'cause a lot's been
going on this summer.
[OTHERS]
Yeah, no joke.
[CHIAKI] Buying it after
school without a preorder
is gonna be tough.
There's no guarantee.
[KAREN] Maybe they'll have
a copy, if you're lucky.
You know, like if
someone cancels.
Right. I know the odds,
but I'm going to try anyway.
I swear to you, I will not rest
until I've bought that game.
In that case, you better be
ready to haul ass outta here
when the bell rings.
[KEITA]
Yup! That's the plan, at least.
Even though it's the fifth one,
you're still bonkers
for the game that much?
[KEITA] Totally. It's
really important to me.
As long as they keep
making them, I'm on board.
I've played a couple Space
Ocean games over the years,
but I don't understand
getting that obsessed.
It might sound weird to say,
but the original one
was sort of a first.
Not like the very first video
game I played, or anything.
But it was the first game where
the plot and the characters
really touched my heart.
It sounds like me with cats!
[KEITA] And the follow-up
title almost felt like
it had been programmed
with me in mind.
I'd played a lot more
famous RPGs by then,
but that one
really hit the spot.
All the elements came
together in a way
that left me feeling breathless!
I know it's silly,
but I almost feel like
I was born to be a Space
Ocean completionist!
[TASUKU, KAREN, AGURI]
Cool.
[KEITA] That's why I feel
like such a dunce
for not remembering to preorder.
But the collector in me can't
bear to just download it.
I promise you, I will buy a copy
of Space Ocean 5
on disc tomorrow!
Even if this quest
should end me,
I will die victorious and
ascend to gaming Valhalla!
I don't think you're gonna
croak along the way.
But I'll be crossing my
fingers for ya, buddy.
[KEITA]
Thanks! I'll take it!
Whatever happens at
that store tomorrow,
I'll give it my best shot
and make you all proud!
[AGURI] Yay! Attaboy, Amano!
Break a leg! Woohoo!
[knocking]
[KONOHA]
Hey, Sis?
Yeah?
Why're you sitting
in a dark room?
Uh! What the heck?
Ah. Sorry for the mess.
I was digging through
my old games
and they ended up everywhere.
Yeah? How come?
I was looking for my
Space Ocean 2 disc.
I forgot about it,
but it's really good.
Wanna give it a try, Konoha?
[KONOHA]
Nah, I'll pass.
So how was the big showdown?
Must've worked out if you're
pulling out old RPGs.
It was a flop.
Keita chickened out
at the last second,
so we're not any closer
to clearing things up
than we were before.
It ended up being nothing
but a gigantic waste of time.
[KONOHA chuckles]
I thought he'd wuss out.
But you can't be too mad.
You're part of why
stuff is so confusing.
You even roped me into it.
[CHIAKI]
I'm really sorry about that.
For what it's worth,
you're being a big help.
So... something you
wanna talk about?
I'm just gonna say it.
I dunno where
you're coming from.
I figured I'd try and find out.
"Coming from"?
What does that mean?
Yeah, like you don't know.
[giggles]
[CHIAKI]
Here's what I do know.
Keita has a girlfriend already,
and they seem pretty happy, so--
[sighs]
Aw, jeez.
Can you at least figure out what
you want outta this whole mess?
It'd help a lot.
Like, come on,
I'm the one who's
stuck having to pretend
to be Nobe and Mono
whenever I see him.
Yeah. I guess you're right.
Do you wanna get closer?
If you do, there's nothing
wrong with that, y'know.
Maybe you just wanna keep
fighting with him all the time?
Or maybe you want the
guy outta your hair.
[gasps]
Hey, c'mon!
It's not like you need to
figure out all this stuff
right here and now!
Okay. I'm calling
it a night, Sis.
I hope you get some rest.
And I'm sorry for
bringing it up.
No. It wasn't a problem.
See ya in the morning.
[CHIAKI]
She called it.
When it comes to Keita,
I... I don't know what I want.
[KEITA]
All right then, Uehara, I'm off!
[TASUKU]
Make it happen.
Honestly, his love
of video games
makes the rest of us
look like slackers.
Well, in that case,
I guess I'm outta here, too.
[TASUKU] So long as Amano and
Tendo are in happy-couple mode,
I'm the only one who's
got Hoshinomori's back!
I need to make sure she
realizes what team I'm on!
An' with Aguri busy,
this is perfect timing!
Okay, then.
Uh! What are you doing here?
Hey, how's it going?
I was hoping we could
talk for a bit.
Talk? Yeah, all right!
But I have to warn you, I still
don't have an answer either way!
It really took me
by surprise, Uehara!
I'm not ready to break
any hearts over this, okay?
[gasps]
[TASUKU]
I get it.
She's still figuring out
how she feels about Amano.
She's not sure either way
if it's worth hurting
Tendo to steal her dude.
Makes sense.
Hey, I get it.
My bad, Hoshinomori.
I'm not tryin' to rush ya.
Don't apologize!
Anyone in your position would
wanna know how I feel!
I'm just sorry to make you wait!
What's up, you guys?
I'm not sure what
I'm interrupting here,
but it looked sufficiently done,
so, whatevs, I'm going for it.
That's cool, I guess.
The thing I was talking
about sorta hit a dead end.
Actually, I'm having a bit
of a dilemma right now,
and I was hoping that
maybe you could help me.
[TASUKU]
Hm?
[ALL laughing]
[AGURI] This is a trap.
And I fell for it!
Check it out! This was her
back in middle school.
Pretty blah, am I right?
Snooze-ville!
Hey, stop!
Crazy what a bit of hair
dye can do for ya, huh?
Whatever, man! I'd hit
the old version, too!
[SARINA, JERKFACES laughing]
Why'd you invite these
random guys along?
You know I have
a boyfriend, Sarina.
So do I. But I don't see
what that's got to do with it.
Wow. For real?
[JERKFACE A]
What'cha talkin' about?
[SARINA]
Just girl stuff.
[JERKFACE A]
Aw, c'mon! Don't be...
[AGURI] I kinda forgot
how mean Sarina can be.
[JERKFACE A]
Hey, Aguri! Tell me somethin'.
I heard you went to some
gamers meet-up thing!
So what if I did?
Why do you care?
Aimin' low, don'tcha think?
[AGURI]
What do you mean?
A thing like that's gotta be
a wall-to-wall nerd
sausage-fest!
[SARINA]
Ew! No kidding!
[AGURI]
Excuse me?
They're totally grabbin' their
joysticks thinking of you!
I cannot believe
you just said that!
[JERKFACE A] At least they're
doin' it to a real chick
and not some, like,
elf or whatever!
So how's it feel to be
queen of the gaming dorks?
What if they, like, touched you?
That stank isn't
comin' off easy!
[ALL laugh]
[AGURI]
You know what?
I'd rather hang out with
the nerdiest one of them
than deal with you meanies
any longer than I hafta.
I'm gonna go now!
We invite you along, and
that's the crap you pull?
What the hell?
I've got nothing to say to you.
I get it.
Your boyfriend must
be one of those
mouth-breather game-nerds
we were laughing at.
Guess again.
Then how come you copped
such an attitude back there?
'Cause it's mean.
What's the problem?
If we're making fun of guys who
aren't even your boyfriend,
why do you give a crap?
Way to white-knight!
I can't believe you brought
down the mood like that!
[AGURI]
You don't know them.
Amano might be a
game-loving nerd
with more consoles than friends,
but he still deserves respect!
Why do you care if I dunk
on some rando, huh?
If the two of you aren't a
thing, then it's all good!
[AGURI]
He's still my friend.
I don't get you.
If that's all you
came out here to say,
I'll be leaving now.
You can mess with your
hair all you want!
You're still the same mousy
wallflower you were
back in middle school!
[laughing]
And I'm super-happy to hear it!
Thanks for the
compliment, Sarina!
[SARINA growls]
[phone ringing]
[AGURI]
Tasuku.
So what's this dilemma you're
all bent out of shape about?
Go on. I think
we're both curious!
I hope it's not awkward
I brought this to you.
Lately I feel like I've been
kind of... kind of... off.
For lack of a better
way to put it.
I mean, ever since I started
going out with Amano,
my skin has been softer
than a baby's buttcheeks!
Everything I eat is way more
delicious than it should be!
The world and all
of its creatures
great and small are beautiful!
[TASUKU]
Yup, she's lost it.
In a perfect world, Amano
and I would get the chance
to hang out every
day after school.
But he ran off to buy
that game today.
So... Uh, I just
miss him is all,
and half the time he goes to eat
with Aguri after class lets out.
You've got it bad for that kid.
[KAREN sighs]
Well, I wouldn't lose any sleep
over the time he
spends with Aguri.
She even told me she
only thinks of the dude
as a high-maintenance kid
brother, so no worries there.
She doesn't like him like that?
Oh, wow. What a relief.
And can you imagine
Amano without his games?
He'd be a disaster.
I don't think you
should be jealous
of the time he spends gaming.
'Cause I think it's part of
what makes Keita who he is.
He acts like a wimp,
but he can be stubborn, too.
Sometimes he puts
gaming front and center
when he should try to level
up a bit more in real life,
but it's not a bad thing.
It's part of why you like him.
Yeah. You're right.
That's classic Amano.
I'm going to have to share
him with video games.
Honestly, I wouldn't
have it any other way.
[TASUKU]
Dammit.
I give her crap, but her
feelings for him are legit.
Sorry, I know it's dumb how much
I've got my wonderful boyfriend
on the brain these da--
What was that for?
I'm calling a time-out on
relationship talk, ladies.
[AGURI]
T-Tasuku?
I didn't think you
were cheating on me
with both of them at once!
[TASUKU]
Ah! Are you kidding me?
Right as we get back to normal?
I can explain!
[crying]
Listen to me!
I only like Amano!
As far as I'm concerned,
Uehara's one of those
NPCs who loads wrong
and he's just teeth,
hair, and eyes!
I second that!
I'm way past the
point where I care
whether or not Uehara
used to think I was cute!
I appreciate you tryin'
to do me a solid, ladies,
but it kinda feels like you're
bustin' my chops right now!
[KAREN, CHIAKI] Nobody asked
for your opinion, cheater!
[screaming]
My boyfriend's being
called a cheater
by the girls he's
cheating on me with!
Save me, Amano! Save me!
I'm sorry.
I guess I kinda got
carried away, didn't I?
It's okay. Really.
It was just a
misunderstanding.
That's right!
Hello?
I'm the dude who just got
slandered by the three of you
at the top of your lungs.
[CHIAKI, KAREN growl]
Oh, yeah!
I called Amano back when I
thought everything was horrible.
False alarm.
I wouldn't worry.
He probably hasn't even
checked his cellphone.
This is the afternoon
he dedicated
to finding Space Ocean .
Yeah. Nothin's gonna
get in the way of that.
Right. Guess I forgot!
[chuckles]
[KEITA]
Aguri!
[CHIAKI]
Huh?
Hey! Look who's here!
Huh? Wait a sec!
What about your message?
You were crying and
yelling about Uehara.
I thought you guys
had broken up.
Oh. About that...
Well, it's funny,
really. Kinda-sorta...
Don't tell me it was
just a false alarm.
You're right!
Everything is fine!
Wow, seriously?
Ugh! This is what I get for
trying to be considerate!
[AGURI] I'm super-duper
sorry. Forgive me!
[KEITA groans]
I've got a question.
How come you're even here?
How come?
Well, you know why.
Aguri called and it sounded
like she was in trouble,
so I rushed over ASAP.
But you were out trying to buy
your favorite video game ever.
That? As soon as I got
her message, I gave up.
This was more important
than some RPG.
[AGURI laughs]
You're all sweaty from
running over here!
Maybe those jerks at the café
were right about you, nerd!
Who are you calling
a nerd, you lunatic?
The only reason I'm here
is because somebody
totally cried wolf about having
broken up with her boyfriend!
[AGURI giggles]
[AGURI]
You're such a dummy, Amano!
I never mentioned a wolf!
I thought Tasuku was being
a snake, but that's different!
[KEITA]
It's an idiom!