[FEMALE STUDENT 3A yelps]
[TASUKU]
Hey, Amano.
Morning, Uehara.
How's it going...?
I'm mad, and I want
my time back!
Remember that game
you talked up?
Turns out it's boring
as all hell!
No way! You played
the Nobe game?
Tell me about it!
[sighs]
[TASUKU] Damn thing
started strong enough.
I'm down for survival horror,
and I was pretty hyped to see
how the stuff they were setting
up was gonna play out.
Then it turned into a fishing
game halfway through,
and I wasn't feeling that
so much, y'know?
But since it was a
recommendation from you,
I thought, "I'm just gonna
power through to the end."
That ending.
Oh, that ending!
[TASUKU] The last shot of the
game was some old geezer posing
in front of a stupid black
bass he just caught!
What the hell did I play?!
Yeah! That's textbook Nobe.
You gotta love it, right?
You outta your mind?
That game is just a bunch of
ideas thrown together.
I wouldn't play that again
if you paid me!
Sorry about that!
The rational part of my brain
is aware that Nobe's games
are a real train wreck.
But there's something kinda
charming about how randomly
the pieces all come together.
[TASUKU]
You're not makin' any sense.
How can I explain?
Oh, I know!
It's like when you fall in love.
There's no logic.
[TASUKU]
Big talk from a guy
who's never gotten
to first base.
[KEITA yelps]
Hey! Who cares what
base I've reached?!
Just because you and Aguri
have probably gotten to
home plate, an' stuff.
Uh!
Or not!
Don't worry about me, v-card!
I do just fine!
What about you and Tendo?
Huh? What do you mean,
me and Tendo?
Haven't you seen her a bunch
since you blew her off?
I'm actually sad about
how little I've seen her.
How little?
Wow, you honestly mean
that, don't you?
Yeah. Though it almost
feels like I see her
out of the corner of
my eye sometimes.
Ah. Never mind.
I guess that's good
enough for now.
Just make sure you don't
pass her by so much
that she forgets about you.
Pass her by?
Wait... like a StreetPass?
Yeah, like StreetPass.
Except not at all!
[phone vibrates]
Uh, sorry, Uehara.
You mind if I help out
with this raid?
Uh, yeah, fine.
I know I'm gonna regret this,
but why is your
username "Tsucchie"?
Well, whenever I'm online,
I like to use a name
other than my own,
just to give it some distance.
My mom's maiden
name is Tsuchiyama,
so I shortened it down.
Oh, I also go by Yama
from time to time.
[TASUKU]
It's a pretty lame back-story.
Hey, that's my mom!
[TASUKU]
Okay, so what about Mono?
[KEITA]
Oh, they're awesome!
We met in-game.
I've been friends with Mono
ever since I started playing.
We've never hung
out in real-life,
but I feel pretty close
to them, nonetheless.
There's something
mysterious about it!
[sighs] Wow, you're gonna need
some training in the off-season.
Otherwise, your rom-com
is like majorly DOA.
Hold on. Rom-com?
Is that an emulator?
Romantic comedy!
God knows it's
never gonna happen
if we leave things up to you.
Yeah. You're right.
A girl like Tendo would never be
interested in someone like me.
Hey, cut it out.
I'm not trying to bust your
chops about it, okay, Amano?
The thing is... I just...
I wanna help you
power-level your charisma
with the ladies, that's all.
Uehara!
You care about my
stats that much?!
What are friends for?
Now let's get you talkin' to
some nerd-girls who are
into the same kind of games
that you are! 'Kay?
[KEITA]
Uh...
All right! That chick
is your target!
Her name is Chiaki Hoshinomori.
They say she'd rather stare at
her handheld than be a person,
so... she's basically you.
Wow, what're the odds?
But I still don't get why I have
to hit on some random girl.
Oh, no ya don't!
It's time for you to sack up
and march in there!
[KEITA] I don't see how
a sack plays into this!
[AGURI]
There you are!
Tasuku! Weren't we
supposed to hang out?!
Yeah, we were, huh.
I'm sorry about that.
Good luck to ya!
I can't wait to hear
how it all goes down!
[KEITA]
Huh?
[TASUKU] Pretend she's an NPC!
You'll do fine!
What?
What did I do to deserve this?
[KEITA] Ohmygod,
they're all staring at me!
[STUDENT 2B] Tendo doesn't
seem herself lately.
[KAREN laughing]
[EIICHI]
Oh, hey Amano!
[yelps]
So, what brings you by?
Are you here to
see Tendo, maybe?
Um, nuh-uh! Not in the least!
Believe me when I say
that she's got nothing
to do with why I'm here!
[KAREN gasps]
Interesting.
What is your reason
for stopping in?
[KEITA]
Uh...
I did drop by to see someone,
but I'm afraid it's not her.
[KAREN]
Whoosh.
All right!
[KAREN groaning]
Ouch.
[KEITA]
Um, excuse me!
[KEITA] She's completely
engrossed in her game.
Hey.
What's she playing?
--[KAREN] Ahem.
--[KEITA] Uh! Uh. Tendo!
Well! Fancy running
into you here, Amano!
[KEITA]
Yeah! Pretty crazy, isn't it?
Is there anything I
can assist you with?
Uh. I'm good, but thanks a lot.
I actually came to Class A
to talk to somebody else.
Oh.
I get it now! Class F
probably sent you over
with some sort of message
you're supposed to deliver!
Ah, good old boring student
government stuff!
What?! No! I mean.
I don't think that's why. Uh?
[TASUKU]
Oh, no ya don't!
It's time for you to sack up
and march in there!
Sack up.
Sack up. Sack up.
That's right!
I came to this room
for the sole reason
of getting to meet
Miss Hoshinomori!
[KAREN gasping]
[KEITA]
Ahh! What happened, Tendo?
--Speak to me!
--[gasps]
[HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS screaming]
Oh, come on!
Very mature, everybody!
Ah. Ah. Ah...
I'm here.
Ah. Ah.
Awful! You're just awful!
Tendo, wait!
Sorry man, I should go.
O... kay.
That was kinda weird.
Well, back to business.
Uh, Hoshinomori?
[gasps] Why, why are
you looking at me?
I... Where do I even begin?
Handheld!
That's Aegis Eight, am I right?
It came out last week.
[KEITA] I should've said
it back at school,
but I'm Keita Amano,
from Class F.
[CHIAKI]
"Amano." Okay.
I guess you like games, 'cause
I saw you playing one and all.
Yes.
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[KEITA]
Making small-talk is torture!
[CHIAKI]
Hey, uh!
Uh?
You're a member of the
game club, aren't you?
Look, I'm very sorry,
but I still have no
interest in joining.
That's my final answer!
Wait! I'm not actually
in the club.
This isn't like a
recruitment scheme.
Honestly, I said no
to them myself.
Uh?
Wait, Tendo tried to
enlist you, too?
Uh-huh.
She invited me to one
of their club meetings,
and I checked it out like
I said I would, but...
But then it turned out
that the club's activities
weren't really what you had
in mind as a gamer, right?
[gasps] That's right!
[KEITA] It's not that
there's anything wrong
with the game club,
but it wouldn't have been
a good fit for you!
How'd you know?
I like playing with people,
and I like to win, but I don't
need to be the best ever.
I'm a gamer because they
make me feel something
that nothing else
in the world does!
Yeah! Ditto!
And if playing with the
club made me feel like that,
I'd join it for sure.
I really hated having
to turn Tendo down
when she asked me to be
a member! But I did!
We both did, because
games are our life,
and we need to be true to them!
Exactly!
[KEITA] And with that,
the two of us broke the ice.
Our shared passion
gave Hoshinomori and I
something to talk about.
[KEITA] Uehara assumed
we'd have a lot in common,
but even he would have been
amazed at how much.
The more we talked and texted
each other, the clearer
it became that we were
two sides of the same coin.
And when the topic was gaming,
she and I were totally in sync!
What we'd played before, how
we'd approach a boss fight.
It was as if we took the words
out of each other's mouth!
[KAREN groaning]
[KEITA] How did you end up
liking Aegis Eight, hmm?!
--Love it!
--Right?!
The whole franchise hits
it out of the park!
You said it!
And the best thing about it!
The very best thing!
--[KEITA] Are the characters!
--[CHIAKI] Is the soundtrack!
[KEITA] So much for breaking
the ice, am I right?
[TASUKU]
Wait, why can't you be friends?
Irreconcilable differences.
Dude!
She's a game-loving loner, it's
like you're the same person.
Yeah.
And, we got along really
well up until then.
When I think back
on it objectively,
she was a lot nicer to
me than you, Uehara.
Just kidding.
I love you the best!
So?
Why'd you get all PVP?
What did she say
that was so horrible?
Believe me, you wouldn't
have let it slide, either.
I'm serious!
Just say it.
Chiaki says moe characters
are a cancer on the genre!
[TASUKU]
You sad little man.
As soon as she spoke
those words,
I told Chiaki in no uncertain
terms how wrong she was!
Lame.
[sighs] Don't get your
boxers in a bunch.
I am the one who made you
talk to this chick, so...
I'll help you two little
weirdos work this all out.
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[CHIAKI] How could you
seriously think that, Keita?!
The Japanese game industry
is drowning in moe ,
while foreign dev teams are
focusing on story and gameplay!
If you look at sales
and critical acclaim,
it's obvious which side
has all the momentum!
It just goes to show how
wrong you are, moe lover!
How dare you say that
about the glory of moe ?!
Like you've never played a
foreign game and said out loud,
"If only these girls
weren't so ugly!"
It's time to drop the charade!
You uptight, seaweed head!
[gasping] Seaweed?!
You guys suck at insults.
It's totally pathetic.
[CHIAKI, KEITA grunt]
This is dumb.
What's it gonna take to
make you guys make up?
Uh. Right!
Maybe it is time to
bury the hatchet!
Well.
Look who drops her ideals when
the cute boy tells her to.
Bravo.
I never said he was cute!
Arguing over video games is
harmless enough, I guess.
But lay off the personal stuff.
Hell, you're right about
Amano being a fan-boy.
[KEITA]
Hey!
[TASUKU] So, weren't you
hype about Aegis Eight
before ya both went
into rage mode?
I guess it couldn't
hurt to ask Chiaki
how far through the game she is.
Um. I guess I could tell you.
If you must know, I got
to the Elven hideout!
Ah! That's where I am, too!
That whole area is one of
the best in the franchise!
I agree!
You never get to see a level map
like that one anymore,
where you can tell they agonized
over every  single detail!
Totally! The way they
show you that the Elves
are bigoted against humans
without ever having to actually
say it aloud is a triumph
of in-game world-building.
[gasps] Mm-hm!
But it pales in comparison to
my favorite part of the area.
But there's just one thing
that keeps that level
from reaching utter perfection.
--That dumb little moe elf!
--That super cute moe elf!
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[TASUKU] Okay!
Aegis Eight was a bad call!
I don't care if you
think we're stupid!
A gamer's opinions
aren't something
you just change willy nilly.
No! They're our creed, and we'll
defend them to the death!
What he said!
Having friends is nice, but
being right is even better!
[TASUKU]
You guys deserve each other.
Uh?
[KEITA]
Girly rage, 12 o'clock.
I'm gonna call it an afternoon.
Anyway, sorry to waste
your time like this.
No! It's okay, really!
I-I don't mind at all.
You clearly know your stuff.
Hearing you talk games was cool.
And who cares if you
have seaweed for hair?
Girls with messy hair are
pretty cute, if you ask me.
Huh? You think
messy hair is cute?
[AGURI screeching]
[KEITA]
Aguri looks like she's about to
crawl out of a TV screen!
[TASUKU]
Whaddya say?
You like games and so does he,
so can ya be buddy-buddy again?
Fine. I'll try my best.
[KEITA] I'm glad he's
clearing the air between us,
but does he have to look like
he's hitting on Hoshinomori
while he does it?
Oh, for what it's worth,
your hair looks good how
you have it now.
But if you cut it short, your
face won't get lost in it,
and that'd be
pretty cool, too.
So, you think I should cut it?
Yeah! If you tried a bit,
you could be cute as hell.
I mean that.
[gasping]
[screams]
[KEITA] Please tell me Aguri
didn't hear him say that
through the classroom door!
This is so bad.
Huh?
[AGURI whimpers]
Hey, Misumi.
Any idea what's going on between
Hoshinomori and Amano?
To be honest, I couldn't
really tell you.
That said, it looks like they're
getting along pretty well,
don't you think?
But how well is pretty well?!
There's a lot riding on this,
Misumi! Cough it up!
You could just ask him yourself.
You know that, right?
[TASUKU] She's pretty
quiet today, for her.
[AGURI]
Hey, uh, Tasuku.
What were you doing over
in Class A before?
Wait. So, you saw all that?
I was, you know...
Is it something you
don't wanna talk about?
What, no way?!
It's nothing like that!
I was tryin' to patch things up
between Hoshinomori and Amano.
Ah. I get it.
Then Hoshinomori was the
girl that you talked to.
Uh...
So, what's the deal with that
Amano guy you hang out with?
What do you mean?!
We just like talkin' about
video games and stuff!
Okay then.
[KEITA] I dunno. I feel like
his new title played it
way too safe across the board.
[KEITA] It didn't have any of
Nobe's usual crazy plot twists.
Huh?
[bell rings]
See ya later.
And hey, keep your eyes
peeled for that one chick.
All right.
[DAIKI] How does a girl that
cute appear outta thin air, man?
It doesn't make any sense.
[TASUKU] They make her sound
like she's Tendo-level hot.
Is that even possible?
[KEITA]
Uehara!
Are you heading home soon?
Yeah. Soon as Aguri
shows up, I am out.
Oh, good.
Huh? What's with that weird
sigh of relief, huh?
Well, I just thought
Aguri might have
said something important to you
on the way home yesterday,
but I guess not.
Nah. It was just
the normal junk.
[KEITA]
Excellent. Never you mind, then!
[TASUKU] Why does Amano
care what Aguri might have
said to me? It's not like they
know each other, right?
[TASUKU]
Hey, Amano.
Do you and her...?
[CHIAKI]
Um, excuse me, Uehara.
[BOTH]
Uh?
[BOTH gasping]
Uh, that's me. Do I know you?
[AGURI]
Uh?
Um, yeah. We've met.
Just yesterday, in fact.
Shorter seaweed.
Shut it! Jeez!
You're such a jerk!
What the--?
Hoshinomori, is that you?!
Uh-huh!
[TASUKU] Wow. I know I
gave her a little advice
about her looks, but I
thought she'd get, like,
10% hotter, not this!
I'm sorry. I guess
this is weird.
Uh. How ya figure?
Well. I mean, yesterday, you
told me I should cut my hair
to be cute, and now
I look like this.
Hey, no problem.
I'm just glad it
worked out, you know?
And it turns out I
was right about you.
You're cute as hell!
[TASUKU]
Cute as hell, cute as hell.
[screams]
[KEITA]
Seriously, Uehara?
Huh?
Aguri?
But are you sure? Like does
this work for me, Uehara?
It's crazy, but my family
didn't recognize me when
I came out for breakfast this
morning, so I was kinda worried.
Whaddya mean, does it
even work for you?
You're a freakin' knockout!
Yeah, do you think so?
[laughs] Thank you
for the compliment!
Hang on. Amano.
Where's he at?
Oh, Keita ran off that
way a moment ago.
After someone named
Aguri, I think.
[gasps]
[KEITA panting]
[KEITA] Crap!
No sign of pink hair anywhere!
[KEITA]
Hey, Tendo!
Ah! It's Amano!
Thank goodness!
I think we got off on the
wrong foot yesterday.
Anyhow! Sorry I
came on so strong!
[KEITA]
Huh? What's she on about?
No! Don't care!
Gotta keep moving!
Tell me something.
Did you happen to see
a pink-haired girl run
by here, maybe?
Cute and ditzy, might've been
bawling her eyes out?
[gasps] Now that you mention it,
there was a sad,
pink-haired girl heading
straight for the lockers.
Uh. I owe ya one!
Wait! Amano!
Yeah, what's up?
You never told me why
you're chasing after her
in the first place!
Y'know! Typical
relationship drama!
[KAREN]
Relationship drama?
There you are!
Ew. It's the guy who
hangs on my boyfriend.
Is that what people think around
here when they see me?!
[KEITA] No wonder they
give me such a wide berth.
Anyway, what do you want?
Oh! Uh, I thought...
I-- I thought maybe you'd like
to go have some tea with me!
Huh?!
[KEITA]
Is it me?
Or does this feel like
I just asked her out?
[KEITA]
So awkward.
This is what I get for just
shooting from the hip.
Hey! So, uh.
Yeah, what?
I think you're operating under
a bunch of assumptions
that might not actually
be the truth.
[AGURI]
Hm?
I don't think there's
anything going on
between Uehara and Chiaki
that's, like, romantic.
But I heard him.
He said Hoshinomori was
"cute as hell" back there.
Oh, that was just a figure
of speech, don't sweat it!
Yeah! And just the
other day, he told me
how you've been looking
super-cute to him lately!
Do you mean it?
[KEITA]
Of course! Cross my heart!
Your boyfriend's crazy
about you, Aguri.
If there's anything
I know, it's that.
He's too good for that sea--
I mean Chiaki, so don't
you worry about her!
Believe me when I say I'm
rooting for the two of you!
[gasps] I'm gonna go get
something else to drink.
I'll be back.
[giggling]
[sighs]
[KEITA]
How did I pull this off?
Oh, there's an event.
I'll send Mono an invite.
[KEITA]
It looked like things
were going to get really
bad there for a sec.
--[crash]
--[gasps]
[AGURI whimpers]
[KEITA]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!