[EIICHI] This town is
full of ordinary people,
living out their ordinary lives.
Must be nice.
I wouldn't know.
Three years ago...
...I suddenly came to, playing
a puzzle game at the arcade,
stark naked, and no
memory of who I was.
I was roaming the mean streets,
when out of nowhere...
[RIKI screams]
Stop it! Let go of me!
[EIICHI yells]
[EIICHI]
I don't know why those two thugs
were trying to nab the girl,
but I sent 'em packin'.
Her parents were thrilled
that she was safe,
and adopted me by
way of a reward.
Can't say who I was before,
but I was Misumi Eiichi
from that day onward.
Don't get the wrong idea.
Just because I had a new family
and a roof over my head,
I wasn't living on Easy Street.
That covert organization
was still gunning for Riki,
and I think I vaguely
remember them
messing with me somehow.
Speaking of Riki,
she blows her top
whenever I mention
the girls at school.
On the bright side,
I recently joined the gaming
club at my new school,
and they're good people.
The training regimen is
tough, but it's paid off.
Encouraged by my
recent improvement,
I signed up for
this year's TVGT,
or Total Video Game Tournament,
to see how far I could get.
One by one, my opponents
fell before me.
If I can win this match,
I'll be in the finals.
[GIRL]
Sorry, not today.
Nice winning streak
you've got there.
A shame if something
happened to it!
Hope you're
ready to lose, Eiichi!
[gasps]
My own sister? But why?
[RIKI]
Curious!
No sign of that Tendo girl
you're always rambling on about.
[EIICHI] That's right. Tendo
had a prior engagement today.
What made you think to
even bring her up, Riki?
[RIKI]
Huh? I just-- No reason at all!
When it comes to video games,
I don't pull any punches.
Not even for you!
I'd expect nothing less.
Hope you can forgive the
beating you're about to get!
[EIICHI] I wonder if Tendo
and Amano are on the bus
at this very moment.
I hope they have as
much fun as I'm about to!
[yells]
As I've told you all before now,
the boys and girls
will be sleeping
in separate rooms on this trip.
Our parents are putting a
lot of faith in us, y'know?
And that means we will all
be on our best behavior
until we're home again.
There will be no
flirting allowed!
Uh, right.
What?
Why'm I'm going
out to this place
if I can't even get
cuddly with Tasuku?
It's a training retreat for
the gamer meet-up group.
I knew you were gonna play,
but I didn't think you were
gonna play the whole time!
That is so boring!
[KAREN] Hey! It's not
boring. It's useful!
[CHIAKI] You said it! We're
gonna have a great time!
I'm a little worried about
this trip, to tell the truth.
[TASUKU chuckles nervously]
[TASUKU] At least Hoshinomori
won't be the odd one out,
since Tendo's putting the kibosh
on the lovey-dovey stuff.
Just gotta say, though,
for a trip where there's
no flirting allowed,
you're pretty dolled up.
What on earth are
you getting at?
It's called accessorizing, and
it's something girls do, okay?
[ALL gasp]
[KEITA]
Too hot!
Oww...
Aw, what's the matter?
Is the water too hot for your
delicate wittle baby toes?
Hey! The water's way
hotter on this side!
Check it out!
Splash war!
[BOTH laughing]
[TASUKU]
Ahem!
Hey, Amano.
Is it true you bought
another random game
that doesn't have
much going for it?
That's basically what I did.
I thought I had stumbled
onto a hidden gem,
but I guess I grabbed a copy
of Elders Hunt by mistake.
I don't think I've heard
of that title before!
Wha'd'ya buy?
[TASUKU] Dude, that game's got
a reputation for being crappy.
[KEITA]
Yeah.
And they won't take it back,
even with the receipt.
That's 6,000 yen down the drain.
[KAREN]
Every gamer has known that pain.
I don't understand.
Why do you pay so much
for all these games?
It seems like a big waste.
[ALL]
Gulp.
I mean, 6,000 does sound
steep when you think about it,
but I know you've
got clothes that are
way more expensive than that.
Well, yeah.
'Cause clothes are
one of those things
you end up using
every single day.
Not the same thing.
You don't need video
games to live.
Thousands of yen,
just flying away.
[KEITA, KAREN, CHIAKI]
No-no-no-no!
Wait a minute!
There are plenty of things that
aren't necessary for survival
that are still tons of fun!
Going to the movies while
you're out on a date,
hitting up the bowling alley,
slowly undressing
Amano with your eyes
while he talks about stuff!
Useless, but you wouldn't get
rid of them, now would you?
I don't wanna see Amano
without his clothes,
so that's out.
Games aren't fun like
bowling and movies are,
so what's your point?
Why the hell would we
bother playing them
if we weren't having fun?
Try to calm down.
Even if games aren't
your own cup of tea,
they're definitely fun for
people who like them.
So you see, in the
traditional sense,
it doesn't matter
if they're useful.
And, yeah, I like
to stare at Tendo
while she's talking
about stuff, too,
but without the naked part.
Hope that's okay.
Oh, Amano.
Way to rock the whole
"no flirting" thing.
[AGURI]
Movies are like two hours,
unless they're about those
little hairy-feet guys.
And bowling is kinda
like working out.
But games go on forever.
You all just sit there,
bleep-blooping your life away.
Those bleeps and bloops weave
a tapestry of high adventure!
Tell 'er, Tendo!
Young people are adrift in
a sea of post-modern dread.
Sure, they're long, but without
games to act as a life-raft
for those born after
the death of truth,
there's nothing left to hold
the soul-crushing ennui at bay!
--That was awesome!
--Way to go!
[AGURI]
Hmm...
Yeah, but if it's all that
great junk you said,
shouldn't you look happy the
whole time you're playing?
I mean, leveling up
or whatever's
a pain in the butt, right?
[ALL gasp]
[CHIAKI] Um! Games are
fun across the board!
So since leveling up is part
of the gameplay experience,
it's gotta be fun!
But if that's true, then why
is it that people pass out
while they're playing sometimes,
right in the middle of the game?
Either it's so boring
they can't stay awake,
or it's so brutal that
it kicks their butt.
[ALL]
Headshot!
[AGURI] Doing the same
thing over and over again
just to get more experience
points sounds pretty blah.
What could ever
be fun about that?
[CHIAKI chuckles]
[CHIAKI]
Oh, but you see,
there are different ways to
multitask when you grind,
and if you do it right,
the time flies by!
[AGURI] Wow! You can do
something else while you play?
Gamers must be pretty
smart to pull that off!
[CHIAKI chuckles]
[CHIAKI] Well, it's a
very specific skill-set.
But it means I'm right.
If leveling up weren't boring,
you wouldn't want something
else to do while you do it.
[TASUKU]
Um, speaking of leveling up,
I think we're way under-leveled
for this nice of a room.
I can't believe we
really get to stay here!
You picked a winner, Tendo!
No kidding! So what
do we do now?
[KAREN laughs]
We came all this way on
a gamers meet-up trip.
There's only one thing to do.
Plug in the ol' PZ4!
I'm so glad you brought that!
They came all this way to do
the stuff they do at home?
[TASUKU]
Woo! Ha-ha.
I am stuffed!
[AGURI]
Hmm...
Looks like new games are pretty
much 6,000 across the board.
Wait! Says this one goes for
10,000! Are you kidding me?
I guess it's got a
book of concept art
and a download code
for launch-day DLC.
Hey, guys, what's DLC
stand for, huh?
It's "downloadable
content" abbreviated.
Launch-day DLC could be costumes
for your characters
to wear in the game.
That is a popular one.
People give 'em real money
so they can play dress-up
with their characters
in some video game?
That's lame.
[BOTH gasp]
Hey! Don't look at me!
That kind of DLC doesn't
interest me in the slightest!
Yeah! I would never!
[AGURI]
Tendo said "that kind,"
meaning you like other
kinds of it, don't'cha?
[BOTH]
If there's a bikini pack,
you better believe
I'm buying it.
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[KEITA, TASUKU]
I regret nothing.
[AGURI] Earlier today, when I
said games were too expensive,
you brought up how real-life
clothes can be even worse.
But if it turns out
you're spending money
on clothes either way,
why not just get 'em
for your own self?
Uh, the characters you control
end up being kind of an
extension of yourself.
So if I buy them a cool outfit,
I'm still expressing
my individuality.
--Uh-huh!
--[KATSUKU, KAREN] Mh-hm!
If you say so.
I'm still not convinced
of this whole
"buying clothes I get
nothing out of" thing.
But! You do get
something out of 'em!
How do I put it?
Ah!
What would you say if
Uehara here surprised you
with the gift of a
really nice ring?
[TASUKU]
Huh?
Huh? If he bought me a ring?
I'd be freaking
overjoyed, of course!
[TASUKU]
Uh.
[KEITA]
So now that you have it,
do you equip it or
leave it in the box?
Your call.
How do I equip it? Do you
mean, like, wear it?
'Cause if they mean the
same thing, then you bet.
[KEITA] And would your love
for Uehara get stronger
as a result of that?
Yeah, I guess I'd love
him even more then.
Not that that's possible,
so whatever, you know?
There.
Then I welcome you to
the ranks of those
who accept the idea of DLC.
Oh, yeah, I get it now.
When you put it like that--
Hey, wait! That's totally
apples and oranges!
[KEITA]
Allow me to clarify, then.
In that example,
Uehara buys you an item
that raises your love
stat when equipped,
and he does it with real money!
Hey! Watch your mouth!
It sounds all weird when
you say it like that!
I understand.
If Tasuku got trapped
in a video game,
and it was impossible
to pull him back out,
I could buy these digital
items you're talking about
to doll him up.
Whoa, time out!
Why are you so chill about me
getting trapped inside a game
in the first place, Aguri?
[KEITA]
That's not all.
You could also change your
player-character's outfits
and then see Uehara's
reaction to them.
Maybe he'd start
blushing, or acting shy.
The sky's the limit with DLC!
Aw! I want costume DLC!
Where do I get it?
Cut it out!
I am not getting stuck in
a damn video game, okay?
As for you!
You don't have to change
what you're wearing
in order to make me all bashful.
[AGURI]
Oh, Tasuku.
Buy a loot box for the
chance to win this snapshot
of teenage love for
a mere 300 yen!
I can win this? I'll
take a hundred boxes!
Right away, ma'am.
Damn it all!
Don't use me as a prop
for in-game purchases!
[laughing]
Hey! Thirty thousand yen to buy
Tasuku's tender moments?
Shut up and take
my money already!
Snap out of the
DLC-madness, Aguri!
Save your money.
They're just catering
to the gatcha addiction!
There's nothing in those boxes
I can't give you for free.
[AGURI]
Tasuku.
Though the odds are 5,000 to 1.
And that's how the free-game
industry stays afloat.
Yeah, it makes sense.
You're very informative.
Oh, stop. It was nothing.
Hey, you guys! I think I
understand video games!
[ALL gasp]
[AGURI]
Mh-hm!
It's so clear!
Games are bull[beep]!
Am I right?
[OTHERS screaming]
[KEITA]
So much for that.
[AGURI]
I was thinking about it more.
Is it true that there are games
where you pay however
much it costs up front,
and then you don't even get
to play the whole thing
without buying something else?
Yeah! People are
talking about it.
"The pay-to-win model
is such a load of crap.
Paid players are unbeatable
in multiplayer mode.
Sometimes the single-player
story isn't even finished.
They rip off the
end of the game,
and then they sell it
back to us as DLC."
[TASUKU] Well, it's not every
studio is greedy like that.
[AGURI] But it says here
that big franchises
do it all the time.
So doesn't that mean
the video game industry
is in some pretty bad trouble?
Uh, not every piece of
DLC is inherently bad.
Aren't you glad
when a show you like
comes out with a bonus episode?
Just a little something
after the plot wraps up?
Yeah. I guess.
[TASUKU]
Amano's right.
Sometimes the players ask
for more content as DLC,
so that's all good.
Ahh.
What kind of content would
you ask for as DLC, Tasuku?
In a perfect world, all
of the girls would get--
Higher difficulty!
That's what I want a dev
team to give me for DLC!
[AGURI sighs]
This hot spring
is like paradise!
The water's so hot,
and the view!
It's out of this world, right?
So right!
But harder difficulty
just means the game
is gonna be harder to
play your way though.
I'm sorry, I keep trying
to make sense of it,
but there's no light-bulb yet.
When you achieve
something tough
that you've put your mind to,
doesn't it feel good?
[AGURI] Yeah, that makes sense
to me, but it's real-life.
Well, when a super-tough
level in a game
is torturing you mercilessly,
it feels just as good
because you know you'll
eventually get through it!
[AGURI]
I'm sorry.
Tell me that one more time,
with fewer words.
Fine. What I'm saying
is pain can feel good.
That short enough for you?
[AGURI]
Wait, this is getting weird.
I thought we were
talking about games,
but I feel like now we
took this hard left turn
into funky sexual
stuff you're into.
Hey, what the hell?
Liking a challenge is
universal to all gamers.
It's nothing sexual! Right?
[CHIAKI]
Huh?
Ahem.
Look, call it whatever.
I want video games to be
more challenging in general.
If nothing else, at least I know
my fellow members of the gaming
club get where I'm coming from.
[AGURI] And now I know that
all four of you in the club
are total pain-loving
masochists.
I never would've suspected it,
but I bet ya sit around looking
at "game over" screens
and getting all tingly, huh?
That is not true!
Well, not gonna lie, I do enjoy
a good "game over" screen.
[AGURI]
Seriously?
Then are all gamers...
pain-loving deviants?
Is my beloved Tasuku
some kind of weirdo?
No, we're not!
Everyone likes different stuff.
Personally, I'm really into
the epilogue after an RPG,
when I find out what happened
to the members of my party.
Okay. I guess there's nothing
too weird about that.
You know what?
I want an epilogue where the
hero and heroine turn into fish,
and everybody freaks out because
they can't change 'em back!
That would automatically become
my favorite RPG
epilogue of all time!
I don't wanna
burst your bubble,
but that sounds super creepy.
Uh. Sorry if I gave you
the wrong idea just then.
I assumed it would be at the
end of a classic fantasy title,
not something more modern-day.
[AGURI] Turning into fish is
weird no matter what, okay?
Why can't they be fish
from the very start?
How come you wanna
mess with the player
after they've spent
all that time with 'em?
[CHIAKI chuckles]
[CHIAKI] Don't be silly,
Aguri. That wouldn't work!
It's the fact that
they've been people
for the last 30 or 40 hours
that packs such a punch
when they go
fish-mode at the end!
The player never sees it coming!
Oh, man.
I've probably talked to
crazy people before,
but this is the first time
I've known it for sure.
[CHIAKI]
Excuse me?
Any self-respecting gamer yearns
for a fish-morphing twist
in the epilogue of their RPGs!
Right?
[KAREN gasps]
[KAREN]
Uhh...
[CHIAKI] I guess if they turn
into something other than fish,
that works, too.
I don't think the kind
of animal's the issue.
[CHIAKI]
Really, though,
DLC is kinda like a spin-off
of the vanilla game experience.
If they're not going to
push the envelope a little,
why even bother?
[AGURI]
That kind of makes sense to me,
but why go so crazy with it?
Why not?
If your favorite manga
had a fish version of it,
you'd wanna check
it out, right?
I like my favorite
manga the way it is!
Yeah, about
genetically-modified fish
that fight cockroach-men on Mars
in order to save the world!
We could call it Aqua-Formars !
Wouldn't that be awesome?
[KAREN]
Leave fish-manity alone!
Oh, wow! That actually sounds
like a pretty good read!
Hey, not to be that girl,
but the heroes in the fish
version of the story
can only survive underwater.
Mars is a desert planet!
Fish-manity is doomed!
[CHIAKI]
They'll be all right!
The point is, DLC should be
completely removed and crazy,
compared to the original story!
Yeah, I see the logic
in all that stuff
you've been going on about,
but I don't buy it.
Huh?
What'cha doin', Tendo?
I don't know what
you're talking about!
I'm definitely not
trying to listen in
on the boys' conversation
or anything!
[sighs]
I think I prefer epilogue DLC,
but nothing too crazy in it.
Know what I mean?
[TASUKU]
Mh-hm.
Then again, there's something
to be said for DLC
that just ratchets
up the difficulty.
How do you live, Amano?
You're terminally vanilla.
What's it matter to you?
When it comes to
wacky sidekicks,
you kinda leave a
lot to be desired.
Well, it's not like I wake up in
the morning striving for that.
And you don't have glasses,
so you can't play the
straight-man, either.
If that's my personality,
why do I need specific
eyewear to qualify?
Why don'tcha try to win
a pair outta some loot box?
That kind of additional
content is boring!
I'll throw in 2,000 yen,
ya big cheapskate.
What if I wanted my
glasses to be nice?
[KAREN grunting]
Having fun over there?
'Cause it's looking pretty cute!
There!
[KEITA]
Huh?
[KAREN screams]
All right. There we go!
If I don't get to,
then no one does!
[TASUKU, AGURI whine]
[KEITA]
Hey, I've been thinking about
the DLC issue some more.
What do you think of one
where the hero and heroine
get to live happily ever after?
[TASUKU]
Dude, where's the gameplay?
Sounds like a light novel.
Oh, that's fair.
But after they've already
survived the events
of the main story,
I'd feel bad tossing
them into more danger
just to give me something to do
when they could be
tending sheep or whatever.
Maybe they want to turn into
fish and tend those sheep.
[KAREN chuckles]
My Amano's too much of a
cinnamon roll for his own good.
[KEITO chuckles nervously]
Okay, I think I understand
how DLC works now.
It's like getting extra toppings
on a pizza you ordered,
or buying dessert after
a really tasty meal.
Well, yeah! That's a pretty
good way to put it.
Then, when people hate the DLC,
it's because the
pizza was crappy,
and they had to pay an
extra 300 yen for sauce,
so they get salty
and go online,
and complain because the
pizza already cost a ton,
so what the heck?
I learned a bunch,
but I still feel like games
are too expensive, y'know?
Something about it just
rubs me the wrong way.
If I shell out 6,000 yen,
I wanna get everything.
Don't hit me up for
more cash after the fact.
Real talk? Nobody likes a mooch.
[OTHERS groan]
Hey, don't be like that!
I'm not trying to hate on this
thing you guys love so much,
but I guess I did.
No, it's fine.
It does hurt to hear all that,
but when games are such an
important part of your life,
it comes with the territory.
Sounds like you guys
are masochistic after all,
like Tendo had said
in the hot spring.
There's a wide spectrum,
and she's at the far end of it.
Here's a hint!
That was the perfect
opportunity for you to say,
"My girlfriend is not a
masochist. That's crazy talk!"
Some of us are,
but if you're looking for
something that we all do,
I think gamers put more time
into our hobby than we mean to.
Sounds like a bad thing,
so how come you look
so nostalgic about it?
[KEITA]
Well, there's this game.
My parents bought
a copy of it for me
way back when I was
in elementary school.
It was over-priced, and the
older game it ripped off
did everything better
for a lot less.
[AGURI]
Jeez, what a waste!
Tell me about it!
They had picked up the
wrong game by mistake.
I didn't have the heart to
tell them they messed up.
Mistaken-identity stories
hit close to home!
[KEITA]
But once I started playing
that crappy, overpriced game,
I actually came to enjoy it.
I played it on and
off for three years,
even though at its best
it was just mediocre.
That's a cute memory,
I'm not gonna lie.
But couldn't you have
had the same experience
with a movie or a
book just as easy?
[KEITA sighs]
[KEITA] I think it only stuck
with me the way it has
because it was a game.
When you play,
you're in charge of the time
and effort you put in.
You can get as emotionally
involved as you want to.
[KEITA]
Honestly?
I can't say if games
are "worth it"
in a technical money-type
sense, y'know?
And you buy some where they're
objectively terrible,
and you're stuck.
But that's the risk you take.
That's why, as a gamer,
all I can do is play every
game I come across,
however I feel like!
Even if nobody else feels that
way or sees my point of view!
That.
Plus, it's always fun
to see how other people
rip into bad games in
their reviews online,
or is it just me?
We all do that.
But every now and then, those
are the ones that stick with us.
We end up having such a
memorable time with them,
it's as if they're worth
their weight in gold.
That's right!
And sometimes it's like
a badge of honor
to have made your way through
a really horrendous game.
It's hard to put a price-tag
on a thing like that.
At the very least, that
crappy game has value to me.
It's worth way more than
what my parents paid for it.
After all we've been through, I
wouldn't sell it for the world.
So after all that, do you
understand a little better now
why they cost so much?
Yeah, I get it.
An' I'm gonna do my best
not to say that they're
overpriced anymore.
It's not about that.
[chuckles]
We're on the same page!
[BOTH chuckle]
Okay!
Now that we all agree,
I think it's time we dive into a
game that puts all those values
we were just talking
about into practice!
I think the five of us are ready
to leave our presumptions
at the door,
and see if Elders Hunt is
as crappy as they say!
[OTHERS] G'night! We gotta
get up early tomorrow!
Aww.
Pretty please?