[crash]
[AGURI gasping]
[KEITA] No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
[beeping]
[TASUKU]
Dammit, Aguri.
Where the hell did you
run off to with Amano?
[CHIAKI]
Hey, uh...
I was hoping that we could
talk about game development
a little bit,
if that's all right?
It might be a nice way to pass
the time while we walk around.
Sure. Go crazy.
Wait. Are you developing a game?
I guess you could say that!
[sighs] Don'tcha think
you'd be better off
having a conversation
like that with Amano?
[grunts]
[TASUKU]
You hate him that much?
Who, Keita? Let's just
say that if he were
in first place in
a go kart race,
I'd gladly crush him with a
flying blue shell of doom.
[TASUKU] That's a really
detailed diss for not caring.
--[phone vibrates]
--Uh! Oh, sorry,
I got a message! This'll
just take me a second!
I can totally see you
playing a mobile game
over your shoulder, y'know.
Well?
Uh! I didn't think the raid
would take this long!
Sorry! Just one more minute!
You are so just
Amano in a skirt.
[TASUKU]
"Mono," huh?
Weird nickname.
Hm... Seems familiar.
Where have I heard it?
Uh! Hold on!
Don't tell me Mono's your
handle in that phone game!
Yeah, does it matter?
I know I'm gonna regret this,
but why is your
username "Tsucchie"?
Well, whenever I'm online.
I like to use a name
other than my own...
My mom's maiden
name is Tsuchiyama,
so I shortened it down.
Oh, I also go by Yama...
[TASUKU]
It's a pretty lame back-story.
Hey, that's my mom!
--[gasps]
--Is something wrong?
[gasping]
[screams]
Uh. My bad!
I just noticed that other
username, Tsucchie.
I wonder what they're
all about, you know?
Couldn't tell ya. All I know
is, I've been good friends
with Tsucchi ever since
I started playing.
I feel like the whole thing
is kinda like a mystery!
I mean, I know we've never
hung out in real-life,
but, I feel pretty close
to them, nonetheless.
Word-for-word what I thought.
[gasps] What's up with you?
[inhales]
[TASUKU] How can two people
be so friggin' star-crossed?!
[AGURI screams]
Man down!
Huh?! What're you
talking about?
Level with me!
How do you really
feel about Amano?!
I hate him even more than
DLC that's cut from
the original game
as an easy cash-grab.
[TASUKU]
That's some serious hate.
So, I just wanna make sure.
It's not, "I hate the guy, but
I'm secretly in love with him?"
Not even a little.
I'd rather bite off
my own tongue
than have to talk that
loser about anything.
Wow. Graphic.
[sighs] Hey, I meant
to ask you before.
Why'd you pick Mono
as a screen-name?
Huh? Oh, you mean my
handle in the game?
I thought it'd be
a nice gesture.
Uh? "Gesture"?
Yup! My mother's maiden
name is Mononobe,
so I shortened it down
for a nickname.
I like to use a name other
than my own whenever
I'm online, to give
it some distance.
Oh, and I use the
name Nobe, too,
especially if I'm talking
about the games I make.
It's nice having a public
face for that sort of thing.
[TASUKU] Do you hear the words
coming out of your mouth?!
I just can't with you geeks!
I'm good. Sorry, folks.
Uehara. What has
gotten into you?
[TASUKU]
Nothing. Don't worry about it.
So, then. Game development.
That's what you wanted
to talk about, right?
Oh. I forgot.
It's just... I'm trying to
figure out which direction
I should take my
next video game,
in terms of the gaming
scene, I mean...
[TASUKU] Seriously,
how the hell are you two
not madly in love
with each other?
The fact that you and
him aren't a thing
makes me wanna
punch a wall!
[sighs] I dunno. But I'm still
rooting for Tendo, too.
Where the hell did Amano go
with my girlfriend, anyway?
[exhales] If only
there was an easy way
to give this slow-burn romance
a swift kick in the ass,
but they don't even
talk to each other.
[TASUKU gasping]
Uh!
[TASUKU]
I'm a genius.
You don't look so good.
[TASUKU] All I could do was
stand there and tremble
at the thought of my solution.
It was perfect. Like, really.
Genius level perfect.
[TASUKU laughing]
[KEITA, CHIAKI]
We're having a meet-up?
That's right!
We're gonna talk about gaming.
It's gonna rock, you guys.
Let's make some noise!
[KEITA, CHIAKI]
Woo...
Work with me here!
Look, you both love video games
more than what's probably
healthy for a person.
However, you're not feeling the
vibe over at the game club.
That's the case for both of you.
[KEITA, CHIAKI]
So?
Both of you need a club
without all the club crap
that goes with it. Behold.
The creation of a brand-new
organization meant just for you!
Here in this room,
we three shall usher in
a new era of game appreciation!
[KEITA, CHIAKI]
Oh. Oh!
[TASUKU]
Like shooting fish in a barrel.
[KEITA] Um. That's great,
except for one thing.
I agree.
[TASUKU]
Which is?
—I don't wanna do it
--if she's gonna be here!
--if he's gonna be here!
[TASUKU] Why are
they so stubborn?!
[CHIAKI, KEITA growl]
[sighs] If you can't be
around each other,
I gotta respect that.
It's a shame you're gonna
miss out on everything
the meet-up has to offer
you guys, though.
Check it. A big part
of this was gonna be
getting to argue
about video games.
--Whoa!
--Argue?
[TASUKU]
Hook, line, and sinker.
[TASUKU] Well, yeah.
Beating someone you hate over
the head with your
opinions is tons of fun.
But, hey, if you guys
aren't feeling it.
[BOTH]
I guess I could stay.
[TASUKU] And sha-bam!
I'm like Cupid-level good.
You two should just
get married now.
[KEITA]
Uh. Wait.
Isn't a three-person
meet-up kind of lame?
[CHIAKI] I agree. Not with him,
but with the concept.
[TASUKU]
Chill. We might have a fourth,
but she's... kinda on
the fence about it.
Sorry I'm arriving
a little late.
Yeah. I had to talk to
one of my teachers.
Wait! It's Tendo?!
I'm just glad ya made it.
Glad to be here! I'm flattered
I got an invitation
to your meet-up
to begin with.
The game club keeps me very
busy, but I'll see what I--
[KEITA]
Something... wrong?
[TASUKU]
Earth to Tendo.
Uh, ah, yeah! I didn't know you
were going to be at the meet-up,
too, Hoshinomori.
Small world, ain't it?
Yeah! Sure is!
But, I hope this isn't weird
with my having turned
you down and all.
Uh, same here. I didn't say
no to make you feel bad.
Nah. It's fine. But, I do
have one question.
[KEITA, CHIAKI]
Mm?
Tell the truth.
Are you... both sitting here
because the other one came, too?
Don't spare me. I can take it.
[TASUKU]
Uh? She really thinks these two
are hot for each other?
She couldn't be more wrong.
That's right.
You called it.
[KAREN whimpers]
[TASUKU]
What are you doing?!
[KAREN]
Um, never mind.
I don't think the gamers meet-up
is a good fit for me, after all.
[TASUKU] Uh. Crap! I need
to get Tendo in on this!
Watching her drool over Amano
while he and his she-clone
are busy hating each
other is comedy gold!
Plus, it keeps him away from
Aguri, not that I'm worried!
Hey, let's not be hasty!
How 'bout you give it a try
and you can decide later
if it's your thing, huh?
[laughs]
[KAREN] Uh, sure. I mean,
I'm already here.
I don't recall you being so
hands-on with people before.
--Is that a new thing?
--Yeah, I guess!
So. What're we talking
about today?
Hoshinomori's trying
to get her head around
her next game
design project.
[KEITA, KAREN]
Huh?
[KEITA]
Oh, wow.
You make games, huh? How cute.
[TASUKU]
Dude. She makes those
weird games you're
always raving about.
[KEITA, CHIAKI]
Hmph.
Those two are always like that.
It's kind of a thing.
Oh, they don't like
each other? Shame.
[TASUKU] Anyway. What part of
it were you hung up on, again?
Right. Here I go.
It's like, I don't
trust my instincts.
I used to. I would just
charge ahead and make
whatever kind of game suited
my fancy at the time.
But when I do that...
[TASUKU]
People think they suck, right?
My games are way more
popular when I play it safe
and give the user-base
what they desire.
I've done it before,
but when I do...
[TASUKU]
Then you think they suck.
Anybody?
[KAREN]
That's a tough one.
What do you have
to say about it?
Uh?
I really don't have
an opinion either way.
--Uh?
--Huh?
What the...?
And the truth comes out!
You don't give a damn
about my games! Do you!
Well, yeah. But I don't
think I said it right.
Wow. Ruthless, Amano.
Think about it, though.
All that matters in the end is
whether the game's what you want
it to be. It's not my call.
Okay. Way to get
yourself outta that one.
Wait! Seriously?
You mean, you don't
hold game developers
to any sort of standard
with their final product?
No. I guess not.
[BOTH gasping]
[CHIAKI growls]
[KEITA]
It's fine.
Make whatever game
you wanna make.
You can't control whether
it's gonna be a hit or not,
but it's gonna reflect what's
inside of you, no matter what.
[gasps]
[KEITA] I mean,
you could follow your muse
and end up with a masterpiece.
Or, you could slap together
something trophy and derivative
and still have it end up
being a lot of fun to play.
My muse...
Uh. Yeah!
I don't even know if
that makes any sense!
But, it's like, there's this
indie game developer
whose stuff I totally love.
You can tell they
give it their all.
There's so much humanity and
care present in every detail.
That's why, no matter
what a designer intends,
popularity-wise,
whatever they come up with
is going to be true
to that person's heart.
Wow. Well said.
That was a beautiful
answer, Amano.
In general, I really
don't care either way
about whatever crap
Chiaki shovels out.
[CHIAKI]
You're a monster!
[TASUKU] Like watching
toddlers slap at each other.
They... fight like
they're a couple!
[TASUKU]
Calm down! It's all good!
You're the reason
Hoshinomori and him
started hanging out
in the first place.
Huh?
[TASUKU] He wanted to learn
how to talk to you, okay,
so he went and practiced
on her 'cause she's a girl.
She's just training wheels.
They hate each other!
Oh! Well, in that case...
[TASUKU] How does he do it,
ladies and gents?
[TASUKU, KAREN laugh]
[KEITA, CHIAKI]
Uh...
[HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS]
Uh?
[gasps]
[TASUKU]
Aguri?
Hey, c'mon! We've got
that thing, you know?
Uh, right! Sorry, guys.
I'll see you later.
Aguri and I have plans!
Together! Yeah!
That's how that works!
A good day to you all!
[TASUKU]
Uh...
[KEITA]
Okay! I'm all set. Let's go!
Whoa. I did not see that coming.
Is that shallow?
I mean, how'd Keita end up
with such a cute girlfriend?
[KAREN, TASUKU]
Huh?
Yeah. Like, did you see him?
They must really
like each other.
Oh, jeez, I'm gonna miss my bus!
I gotta go! See ya later!
[footsteps]
[TASUKU gasping]
[KAREN gasping]
Thank you for the invite,
but I think I'm done
with the gamers meet-up
for the rest of forever!
Right there with ya, Tendo!
I came up with the damn thing,
and I never wanna do another
one as long as I live!
[AGURI wails]
[KEITA]
I'm really sorry. Honest!
I feel like this is
my fault, somehow.
[AGURI]
'Cause it is, dummy!
Why is this happening?
You said there wasn't a problem!
That nothing was going on with
that hussy and my Tasuku!
You sat right there and told me
that he's crazy about me!
Yeah. That rings a bell.
Yeah! You even said you were
rooting for me an' Tasuku,
so I bought you a soda because
I was in a super good mood
right then, and this is
how you pay me back?!
Uh, it wasn't that expensive,
but point taken.
[AGURI] How come things
are getting worse?
You don't know anything,
so why did I trust you?!
Lemme go! I! I need my ears!
[KEITA grunts]
You suck at this!
What happened to her
being cute was just a
figure of speech, huh?
You told me all sorts of stuff!
"Oh no, Aguri, she's all shy!
It's fine! You got this!"
So why's she cute
now, mister?
Well, the cute thing
is kinda new.
[AGURI wails]
[WOMAN 5A]
What did he say to her?
[WOMAN 5B]
That poor girl.
[AGURI]
You remember, right?
That thing you told me
after all that stuff
you've been wrong about?!
Uh...
"I've made up my mind, Aguri!
I'm gonna help Uehara
come to his senses, no matter
what it takes!" That!
You were almost kinda
manly when you said it.
I wasn't expecting you
to be all tough and junk!
Oh. Well, I try.
[AGURI]
Tell me, then. What's he doing?!
How come my boyfriend is going
to all this trouble to start
a gamer meet-up if it's just him
an' you an' two cute girls?!
I'm sorry. Could you two
try and keep it down?
[BOTH]
We'll be quiet.
[DINER CROWD chattering]
[KEITA]
I knew he was popular,
but I'd never have guessed
he was such a player.
[TASUKU, KAREN laugh]
It's not like I didn't
have suspicions.
Part of me thought
that maybe Tasuku
never liked me to begin with.
And you? Do you still feel
the same way about him?
Even though he might
feel differently?
Duh! Of course I do!
I just think you'd be happier,
y'know, dating somebody
who likes you as much
as you like them.
[laughs] Romance isn't
logical, you big nerd.
[KEITA]
Uh?
One day you fall in love.
An' there ya go!
[gasps]
[AGURI] Just happens.
It hits you outta left field.
An' sometimes it hurts.
Sometimes, you realize
that they didn't fall.
[gasps]
Hey! Look, I swear, Aguri,
I'll do everything in
my power to fix all this!
[gasps] Thanks, Amano!
Let's give it our all,
both of us!
Right!
[KEITA, AGURI squeak]
Chiaki!
Uh! It's the man-eater!
[KEITA] Wait right here,
okay? I'm on it!
[inaudible]
What happened out there?!
You can rest easy.
I told her in no uncertain terms
how perfect of a couple
you guys are.
Yeah?! Like how'd you say it?
I told her that you're the
most thoughtful girlfriend
in all the world! And that your
beauty and your personality
come together to form
one perfect package!
Yeah! So there! Bam!
There's no way she can
have any confusion
about you and
Tasuku's status now!
Wow! Good job, Amano!
You knocked it outta the park!
[laughs] Glad to do it.
Though it's kinda weird
how she reacted.
"Well, good for you."
I guess she just felt like
killing the messenger, y'know?
But all's well that ends well!
Everything's gonna
be fine again!
Okay. I've made up my mind.
I'm gonna help you talk to
Tendo like a human being!
Yeah, it'll cut into my Tasuku
time, but y'know what?
You're worth it!
You would... do that?
Thank you so much!
You're smart and I'm cute!
Together, we're unstoppable!
So, whaddya say?
I'm in! You and me, partner!
[TASUKU]
Don't sweat it.
Like anything would ever happen
between Aguri and Amano.
They only even know each other
because they both have
me in common, right?
Look at how different they are.
She's a ditz and
he's a pushover.
I mean, he probably just
chatted her up to be nice.
No, think about it!
What if they're so different
that they're actually
kind of the same? Oh crap, dude.
They could be hitting
it off right now!
Wait, why do I even
care so much?
He's a giant nerd!
Of course he's not gonna--
But what if I'm wrong?
Aguri fell for me back
when I was a giant nerd!
What if that lame little geek is
sweeping my girlfriend off her
feet right this very second?
Nah, that's crazy.
[laughs nervously]
I'm sorry. You're a sweet guy,
but I think I'd rather keep
our relationship platonic
if it's all the same to you.
[gasps]
[KEITA]
Uh. It was a dream...?
[KEITA sighs] This third
play-through is a beast.
When I use that strategy
on the others, it works.
So, what gives?
[KEITA] Of course it'd be
the girl who looks like Tendo
that cuts me to shreds.
Thanks a lot, life.
[MALE STUDENT 5A]
See ya later.
[FEMALE STUDENT 5A]
I'll text you after I'm done.
[TASUKU]
Trust me, dude.
You don't wanna put any
of that into practice.
[KEITA]
It can't all be useless!
Sure, they're all
scripted encounters,
but I'm using them
to try and prepare
for real-world
conversations with Tendo!
Right?
Look, I'm about to
tell you something
that's gonna shock you down
to your dating-sim lovin' core.
[KEITA]
Uh. Oh, hey! Look at the time!
Tell me later, kay?
You can play dating-sims till
you're blue in the face...
[KEITA]
No! I'm not listening!
[TASUKU] ...but they don't
simulate real relationships
in any way, shape, or form!
[KEITA]
They're all my waifus!
Here's a thought.
Why don't you start worrying
about how to deal with Tendo
instead of leveling up with
a bunch of two-D ladies?
"Deal with"?
Yeah, you know. Make a move.
I'm not getting any younger,
and I wanna see how
this all plays out.
What are you talking about?!
That's a boss fight.
I haven't unlocked all
the special abilities yet.
Until I can figure out
how to talk to Tendo,
I'll probably just mess it up.
Are you serious?
[KEITA]
Of course I am.
[sighs] God, you're so naive.
Okay, from my perspective,
it seems like you're already
talkin' to girls just fine
without making too big
a jackass of yourself.
Huh?!
You rag on Hoshinomori
like she's a guy.
And you... talk to Aguri.
You an' Tendo were hangin'
out at the arcade, right?
Wait, we hung out?!
You are so dumb.
[KEITA]
Yeah! Maybe.
But we were competing,
so it doesn't count!
Sorry, man. I know it's like
the end of an era for you
or whatever, but you're friends
with some real-life girls now.
So it's time to pony up, got it?
[KEITA]
Are you sure Tendo's my friend?
[KEITA] Doubtful. What if
she's just buttering me up
to get in good with
her true target, Uehara?
You hung out.
That's like 90% of what
friends do, you lame brain.
[sighs] Maybe that's true for
most people, but this is Tendo.
Look, I'm fully aware
she's stupid hot,
but she's a human being
like the rest of us.
Yeah, I get it, but I'm
so beneath her notice,
it doesn't make any sense to me.
Get over it, man.
Maybe you weren't on her radar
so much before you
dissed her club,
but now you've been
working that social link.
If she hates you that bad, why'd
she go on a walk with you?
It was a fluke that
she bumped into me!
She probably only asked
to be polite, y'know?
[TASUKU]
Polite?
Ah, what the hell!
It's odd. They're
my relationships,
but in a way,
you're more invested
in my success or
failure than I am.
Well, that's what
friends are for.
You're way too good to me!
I mean that!
[sobs] Thanks for taking
me under your wing!
My life just hasn't been the
same since I met you, Uehara.
How about you save those
lines for the ladies?
[TASUKU, KEITA]
Uh?
Uh, hey guys! You know what?
I have somewhere less
awkward to be! So!
I'm just gonna go there, and...
I swear I didn't see anything!
[TASUKU, KEITA]
Mm?
[TASUKU]
Hm?
Aw, FML! Meet-up's
cancelled. See ya later!
Hey, come back!
It's not what it looks like!
We were just talkin'
about dude stuff!
What?! Wait,
why'd they run away?
I need to call Aguri
on the double!
This sucks! I don't
get any of this!