[KONOHA]
If you looked up "model student"
in the dictionary, you'd
probably find a picture of me.
I like being depended
on, being liked.
And I don't mind
going the extra mile
to make sure that people do.
Not to brag, but I have
a lot of talents.
Although, being pretty good
at a bunch of stuff
isn't as awesome as
you might assume.
Whether it's sports
or academics,
I always rank among the
top handful of my peers.
That said, I'm never the
absolute best at anything.
When the dust clears,
someone else inevitably
walks away with the prize.
So you can imagine my
shock when I was elected
to serve as student
council president.
It felt so good to win
for a change, y'know?
Finally, I was at the
top of the heap.
But the green-eyed monster
reared its head again.
Compared to Karen Tendo,
I felt like some sad-sack
who happened to get lucky once.
I know that jealousy is
a waste of my time;
it doesn't make anything better.
Still, how am I
supposed to be chill
about her outshining me at
all the stuff I try to do,
when everything comes
to her so easily?
That's the problem. I can't.
[KONOHA]
If there's no other business,
then let's call it a day.
Thank you for a great meeting!
[STUDENT COUNCIL]
You too, Miss President.
Guess we'll be
heading out now.
Try not to overwork
yourself too much, okay?
[KONOHA] I'll be fine.
Have a good walk home!
The scent of pure, innocent
maidens, and it's all mine!
[laughing]
Student council is a
hundred percent hot ladies!
It's like they're my harem!
[gasps]
Oh, crap! I forgot!
No time for chair huffing!
[laughing]
[KONOHA] I'm rocking
the perfect disguise!
Behold! The bearded rando!
But my real disguise
goes deeper.
It's true. That of the
"innocent school girl."
In my heart of hearts,
I'm nothing but a thirsty,
dyed-in-the-wool,
totally irredeemable...
[KONOHA]
...hentai-game super-fan!
And just like that,
I've found it!
The newest title in the
Build series by Gagi!
They do such a legit
job with the plotlines,
you feel like you've earned it
once the girls
finally get freaky!
[chuckling]
[KONOHA]
Hm?
[KONOHA] Maybe I should
get a console game,
just to balance things out.
[chuckles]
[STUDENT COUNCIL C] Yeah,
if Karen Tendo went here
instead of Otobuki, she'd have
won student council president
by a landslide.
[STUDENT COUNCIL A]
I know, right?
But Konoha's cool. Like,
she gets the job done.
Oh, this game is
probably more my speed.
[KEITA] You're really sticking
with the game club.
I admire your dedication.
Way to go, Misumi!
[KONOHA]
Those shirts they're wearing...
They go to the same
high school as Tendo!
Aw, man!
Pretty boys like him are
like catnip for my soul!
But the other one's just meh.
Like those bland protaginists
you always see in dating-sims.
You know him?
[KEITA]
That guy? I hope not.
[KONOHA]
Uh! That was close!
Can you maybe recommend me some
good dating sim games, Amano?
[KONOHA]
Say 'em loud!
Okay.
But this isn't a conversation
I'm used to having
with anyone else,
so I hope you don't think
my picks are lame.
I promise I won't judge you.
Everybody is going to
have his own favorites
when it comes to
this sort of thing.
Well, I'm pretty sure I
like the same sort of stuff
as everyone else.
Nothing too out-there for me,
thank you very much.
[groans]
[KONOHA]
Jeez, what a lightweight.
This Amano guy needs to sack
up and start naming names.
So then, were there any titles
you've already heard of
that you were maybe wanting
to know more about?
[EIICHI]
Hmm...
I did do a little
research on my own
the other day to prep for this.
Ah!
People were flipping
their lid about this one
on the internet, weren't they?
[KONOHA] Yeah, that game's
got a pretty good rep.
Nice an' safe.
It's an absolute masterpiece!
I went to school
tired for a week
from staying up
late to beat it.
[EIICHI]
Goodness!
Well, if this has your
stamp of approval,
I think I'll go
ahead and buy it!
[KONOHA]
Done already? Boring.
[KEITA]
Whoa! Wait a second!
Just because I adored it,
doesn't necessarily mean
you'll feel the
same way about it.
Oh, you think so?
[KONOHA] Ugh. You
wishy-washy little cockroach!
Just to confirm it.
You wanna know the difference
between a bad dating-sim
and a good one, right?
No one who's a part of the
club is well-versed enough
in these games for
me to ask them.
[KEITA]
Hmm...
I got it! Hang tight for a sec.
[yelps]
[KONOHA] Pick one already
so I can drool in peace!
I bet you're the sort
who takes an hour
to name their character at
the beginning of a game!
[KEITA]
Ah! Found it!
If you're really depending
on me for a recommendation,
go with Rainbow Court !
[gasps]
I don't think I've ever
heard of that one.
[KONOHA]
Of course you haven't.
It's almost prehistoric
in video game years.
And even back then, it didn't
exactly set the world on fire.
I'm afraid they didn't
sell that many copies,
even back when it was brand new.
[KONOHA]
You see?
[EIICHI]
So why'd you pick it?
I, um, I had a lot of fun
playing through it. That's all.
[gasps]
Cool.
Oh! But there's no pressure
to go with that one.
Whichever you pick is fine!
I figure if I can
talk up anything,
then it might as well
be a hidden gem
that could use a
chance to shine, right?
It's like, when a quality
title gets the cold shoulder
from everyone just because
now the art style
might be a little bit outdated.
I don't know why,
but stuff like that just
really gets to me.
I guess I treat video games
as if they're people.
I'd rather root for the underdog
who never got a fair shake,
than cheer for the one who's
winning the race by a mile.
Uh! I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to
go off on a rant
about some ancient software.
But that said,
I feel like Rainbow
Court is still one of
my top three favorite
games of all time.
That's how much it meant to me!
Back then...
[KONOHA]
Hold on. What's wrong with me?
Why is this so... touching?
In that case,
I'm gonna put my money on the
underdog this time around.
[door opens]
[CHIAKI] Konoha? I didn't
know you were home.
Yeah. For a while.
[CHIAKI] Look here. And
where'd you pick this gem up?
Stop! Put it down!
[CHIAKI] You never told me
you liked these kinda games.
It's not even mine.
I'm borrowing it!
[CHIAKI] So why do I
see a price tag then?
Just give it back
already! Come on, Sis!
[TASUKU] So Amano and
Aguri tied the knot,
right after they
graduated from college.
Like clockwork.
We all told 'em we were happy
for 'em, 'cause it's what ya do.
Three cheers for the lucky
couple, et cetera.
That's the outside.
On the inside, we're
conflicted as hell.
Hoshinomori inhaled
her body-weight in cake
so she wouldn't have
to congratulate Amano.
Tendo and I didn't OD on
dessert, so that's a plus,
but it still drove us nuts
to watch our hearts' desires
heading into the big
penalty box of matrimony.
The ceremony was held
at a reception hall
not far from our
old high school.
Looking back, those years
were a real crap-fest
as far as our group dynamic.
[TASUKU]
Or none of that happened.
It's a no-brainer.
You cram everyone
together in one room
and talk until stuff gets fixed!
Why are you being
such a dummy, huh?
It's not like I spun a
seven on purpose, Aguri!
[TASUKU] As solutions go,
it's pretty damn obvious.
And it's not like I hadn't
figured it out way before now.
With so much
weirdness going on,
it had been tough to get all
five of us in the same place.
Finally, though,
a stroke of luck.
[CHIAKI]
Hey, you guys.
Take a look at this photo
my mom texted me!
[TASUKU] The Love-Love
Game of Half-Life ?
[CHIAKI]
Cool, huh?
I guess my mom won it in a
contest at our supermarket.
Cool.
There's an article
about this online.
It's a new board game all
about romance, right?
[CHIAKI] Uh-huh, I think
it sounds kinda fun!
But I guess we'd need
more people, huh?
Ah. That is a challenge
with board games.
Deal me in.
It should be doable
with three of us.
We can make it an official
gamer meet-up activity.
Do you think so?
In that case, would you
like to come over?
Though I'm not really
sure if I want Keita
knowing where my place is.
What's that supposed to mean?
[KEITA, CHIAKI growl]
[TASUKU]
Not this again.
[chuckles]
Hey, so here's an idea.
How 'bout we get
more people to play?
The more the merrier, y'know?
[CHIAKI]
Any suggestions?
Actually, I do have
somebody in mind
I think would be a perfect fit.
Is their name Tendo?
[TASUKU] She is a gamer.
Sling her an invite, Casanova.
Why me, huh?
Wow, the thought of
Tendo coming to my place,
it's ever-so-slightly
nerve-wracking.
In that case, why don't we
have Aguri come over, too,
and take the pressure off?
She's gotta be
better at board games
than she is at video games!
[CHIAKI] Oh, that's a
good idea. Thank you!
You're surprisingly
enthusiastic about all of this.
[TASUKU]
Mh-hm.
Ha-ha! Finally!
Everybody in the same
place at once!
If we can just to each other
for five friggin' minutes,
we can get all this hashed out
and put this weird love-pentagon
out to pasture already!
At least, it sounded
like a solid plan.
[TASUKU]
The so-called couples
are all sitting away
from each other,
'cause everyone's
wound so tight.
Which is fine I guess,
since it means we can't
fall back on chit-chat
with our significant others.
'Kay, so it's my turn to
move now. Right, you guys?
Here goes nothing.
[TASUKU]
All you do is spin the spinner,
move your piece
that many squares,
and do whatever it says.
It doesn't require any thought,
so you end up talking
about whatever,
which will be the perfect chance
to start dropping
some truth-bombs.
I was so sure my plan was
foolproof, even for this crowd.
And yet...
[AGURI]
One, two, three.
"Newlywed life is going great!
You get pregnant with your first
child on your honeymoon.
You and your spouse
receive 3,000 yen
in gifts from everyone."
[TASUKU]
This game is such BS!
What the heck?
We've been married for a minute
and now you're pregnant?
Hey! You weren't complaining
during the honeymoon part!
This is at least half
your fault, mister!
[sighs]
[TASUKU] Lookin' back, maybe
this Love-Love Game of Half-Life
wasn't the best idea.
The student part of
the game kicked off
with Amano and Aguri dating.
Meanwhile,
Hoshinomori can't land
a steady job after graduation,
and works a bunch of temp gigs.
And then there's Tendo...
Well, time to find out what
life has in store for me!
[KAREN]
Eight.
Let's see.
"Your crush gets married, and
you become more focused on work.
Fifty-thousand yen
in extra income."
[chuckles]
Look at me. I'm so rich.
Isn't that awesome?
[TASUKU]
Tough break, Tendo.
You deserve better, but
Half-Life is a harsh mistress.
That happened.
Guess it's my turn.
[TASUKU]
It's the marriage space.
[TASUKU] When you land here, you
give the spinner another whirl.
All players get numbers,
and whatever it lands on,
you can force that
person to marry you.
If I get a one or two,
I can start over with Aguri,
and Amano gets kicked to
the tiny cardboard curb.
I got a lot riding
on this, spinner,
and not just in
the game, either!
Come on. Come on. Do me a solid!
Dammit!
Uehara! This is such a big step!
[TASUKU] What's that look for?
I just spun the damn thing!
[CHIAKI] Um, my turn now!
I hope I land on something good!
[CHIAKI]
Two.
It says: "Your partner
has cheated on you.
You are forced
to pay their lover
to get them out of the picture.
You and your spouse
lose 5,000 yen."
Oh, no.
[TASUKU] Okay. Enough
with the death-stares.
[KEITA] It's time for
me to spin the wheel!
Okay. Wish me luck!
Oh, five!
One, two, three, four, five.
All right.
"Your lovey-dovey newlywed
life reaches high tide.
You bust your bed getting busy."
I can't believe you actually
broke the bed, you horndog!
Who are you calling a horndog?
We could've broken the bed
doing it the regular
way, y'know?
"Doing it the regular way"?
That's how you
describe our love-life?
[KEITA] Wait! I didn't
mean anything bad by it!
I just assumed that we--!
Shut up.
[KEITA, AGURI]
Sorry about that.
Anyway, I guess
it's my turn again.
Nine. Uh, let's see.
Not again.
[TASUKU]
These kids are doomed.
They're going to "newlywed"
their way to the poorhouse.
I'm not even jealous anymore.
You lovey-dovey bastards.
Wow! Hope my luck is better!
"Your love-interest
won't even look at you,
but you're popular
with your clients."
Oh, hooray.
[TASUKU] If I've ever heard a
"hooray" more devoid of life,
it sure isn't coming to mind.
Yeah, she may be raking
in the big blue bucks,
but she's gonna be
spending it all
on in game therapy at this rate.
[spinner clicks]
Four.
Let's see.
"You cheat on your partner
with their sister.
There is bloodshed. Lose
a turn to the carnage."
That was probably just my
little sister closing the door.
Oh, your sister's home?
That's cool. I had no idea!
[TASUKU] Man, art is
really imitating life
at this exact moment in time.
Hey, my turn again already?
Okay.
"You realize that your
soulmate is someone
other than the person
you married.
Once you're finally aware
of this fateful connection,
you fall for that person,
head over heels,
which distracts you at work.
Lose 3,000 yen."
That square seems
really specific, huh?
[KEITA laughs]
It's kind of hard to
picture you of all people
having some unknown soulmate.
Stop being rude, stupid!
[TASUKU] She's arguing with her
soulmate about soulmates!
What the hell?!
It's like the Love-Love people
looked at their half-lives
and wrote that square
especially for them!
That little plastic spinner
is no toy, you guys!
It's an agent of Fate!
Something wrong, Uehara?
Nothing's wrong! Why
would you say that?!
Just take your
damn turn already!
Yeah! I can do that.
How'd I land on the same dumb,
overly-specific
square as Chiaki?
Love-Love Game of
Half-Life knows all!
Yeah, my bad.
I'm just so excited that
the five of us are together.
I couldn't help myself there.
You too, huh?
I've never sat around playing
board games with anyone before,
but I'm having a great time.
Oh! That means it's
my turn again, huh?
I can't wait to see
what goes down!
Hey, I got an eight! Not bad!
That's a lot of spaces!
The pink one says:
"The person you'd been seeing
before makes a move on you."
Ah! I'm so glad!
There's more.
"But your devotion for your
current partner is unwavering!
You turn your soulmate down
without a second thought,
and recommit to your marriage.
Your love is rewarded in
the form of another child."
[KEITA yelps]
Let's see if I can
turn my luck around.
Great, now they're
not even trying!
[knocking]
[KONOHA] Hey, Sis. Can
I borrow you for a sec?
Sorry, you guys. I shouldn't
be gone for too long.
Wanna take a breather?
[CHIAKI]
What's going on, Konoha?
[KEITA]
You know, I'm kind of curious
about Chiaki's little sister.
Really now? Would you like to
walk that statement back?
Wait, no! I didn't mean
it in a weird way!
All I meant is I couldn't see
her. I swear I'm innocent, sir!
[TASUKU, AGURI]
Sir, huh?
[phone buzzes]
Ah. Must've been a
push notification.
There's an event starting
today in my mobile game.
[TASUKU]
Yeah, I forgot.
He and Hoshinomori
both play that.
She's probably getting the same
heads-up right about now.
Aw, son-of-a bitch!
What if she sees him
checking his phone,
and then they start talkin'
about the game to each other?
[TASUKU]
There. Better.
[KEITA] Uehara, why are
you making that face?
What face? Everything's fine!
[TASUKU chuckles]
[KEITA]
Huh?
[KAREN]
Well!
That actually looks pretty fun.
Yeah. Super fun. I am so sorry!
I'm not that great
at multitasking!
Don't stop playing for my sake.
I'll just watch you do
your thing. Go ahead.
[TASUKU] Good thing she
distracted him. Thanks, Tendo.
I've been watching.
Doesn't it look like those
two are really starting
to hit it off?
Yeah, I guess so.
[AGURI] Amano can be
a dummy sometimes,
but I'm so glad things
are working out for him.
You are?
Well, of course I am.
Aren't we all?
Uh, yeah. Sure. You called it.
I just thought that...
Huh?
You've been hangin'
out a lot lately.
It feels like you and Amano
are joined at the hip,
and I wanna know how
you feel about him!
Don't hold back!
Uh! How do I feel about Amano?
Oh, gosh.
It's like having
this cinnamon roll
of a little brother
who's kinda derpy.
Yeah!
And he doesn't know how the
real world works at all,
but he's got a
girlfriend somehow.
He and I haven't been
friends super-long,
but I think he's a good guy,
and I'm on his team.
Awesome.
What're you doing?!
That came outta nowhere!
Do I need a reason to hold
my own girlfriend's hand?
No, it's fine. You just don't
do it very often, that's all.
Is it okay that Tendo's here?
Tendo?
I don't get it. What's
she got to do with us?
Huh?
But if that's true, then...
Yeah. That's a good point.
Tendo doesn't have anything
to do with us. Right.
This sucks.
It doesn't even feel like
a raid without Mono here.
Mono? You've never
mentioned them before.
Ah. That's my mistake.
They're an online friend of
mine in this mobile game.
Honestly, their companionship's
top-notch in a lota ways.
Oh, great. A close friend of
indeterminate gender online.
Ya got any more of 'em?
Not many, but the few that I do
are among my most
important ones.
That's interesting.
And what do these mysterious
internet friends know about you?
Oh. Not a lot.
I use different nicknames based
on whatever I'm doing online.
Sorry that took
so long, everyone.
[KEITA] But most of the time,
it's one name or the other.
Honestly, 90% of
my conversations
are with two people.
[KEITA]
When I'm online raiding,
I play under the
handle "Tsucchie."
That's the name my friend
Mono would know me by.
Other times, I'll be
posting back and forth
on the forums with this
awesome indie game developer
known as Nobe.
In those cases,
I go by the name Yama.
[KAREN]
Just the two, then?
I assumed you might be
better at talking to people
when it isn't face-to-face.
[KEITA] 'Fraid not.
Thanks for the vote...
Is something wrong, Tasuku?
[TASUKU]
God, what a train-wreck.
It's just that Mono and
Nobe are special to me,
each in their own unique way.
It's almost like they get a part
of me that no one else does.
[TASUKU]
If I weren't face-palming,
I would see a girl who finally
bought herself a ticket
to Obvious-town
for the big parade,
only to miss the end
of it by five minutes.
Hoshinomori's heart
just stumbled
into a checkpoint unprepared,
and now she's eyeballing a
fight she can't hope to win.
That of the too-late soulmate.
So bored.
Isn't there anything
fun to do around here?
[gasps]
[KONOHA] What's wrong, Sis?
Why're you down there?
Yama.