[cicadas buzzing]
[ticking]
[ticking continues]
[KEITA] Some people are just
in a league of their own.
[SHOPKEEPER 1A]
Ah, good morning!
[KEITA] Maybe they're
your favorite idol,
or an athlete that's playing
at the top of their game.
[KEITA grunting]
[KEITA] Maybe they're just...
pixels on a screen.
[KEITA] Most of the time, all we
can do is admire them from afar.
I mean, it's not like
we're face-to-face.
Heh.
[KAREN]
Um, excuse me.
[KEITA]
Uh...
[KEITA] That's why,
when the cutest girl in school
appeared out of nowhere,
and started a
conversation with me...
[KAREN laughs]
[KEITA]
...your humble narrator,
Keita Amano, went
into panic mode.
We haven't talked
before, have we?
I'm a student at Otobuki
High School, like you are.
My name is Karen Tendo.
[KEITA]
Karen Tendo.
She's a second-year, but if
popularity were Everest,
her flag would be on top.
Good morning!
Hey, Tendo!
It's such a nice day out, huh?
[KEITA] She's smart, beautiful,
even good at sports.
How could one person have
so much going for them?
That should be illegal!
[KEITA] Even though she's not
famous, as far as school goes,
Tendo's the closest thing to
a celebrity that we've got.
It's like... she's the queen
of whatever she touches.
Meanwhile...
So, uh...
Uh?! I'm sorry!
I'm Amano! F my class.
Ah! No! I mean, I'm in Class F!
[KEITA screams]
What is wrong with me?
I'm acting like I've got
a harem of hug-pillows!
Nice to meet you, Amano.
O... kay.
[KAREN] Now that we've met,
let's clean these up.
[KEITA]
Wait, what?!
[KEITA] Seriously, what
the heck is going on here?
Is this, like, "Give the Nerd
a Heart Attack" Day?
[KEITA]
Or maybe, she actually--
[KAREN]
So, you're into this stuff?
[screams]
Games, I mean.
[KEITA]
Oh, yeah! Games in general!
Games in general are awesome!
Not that one you're
holding in particular,
because I don't really know
anything at all about that one!
[KAREN]
Hm?
I, uh, didn't mean to yell.
My bad.
[KAREN] This is one of the games
you were holding earlier, right?
What's it about?
[KEITA]
Hm? Ahh! No, don't--!
[FEMALE GAME VOICE 1A]
" Golden Memories ! Va-voom!
A dating-sim filled to the brim
with blonde beauties
for you to choose from!
And jiggle physics."
--I love it!
--[screams]
Games in general,
remember? Not that.
Games in general, of course!
Yeah! Not the one
where the whole idea
is to get the blonde girls
as naked as possible, right?
[KEITA]
Orbital strike.
Target: Keita Amano.
[KEITA]
I play a lot of stuff.
An' I heard Golden Memories
actually had some
pretty cool game mechanics.
Y'know, underneath
all the fan-service.
So, I wanted to take a
look at the back cover,
and see what all the
fuss was about.
Yeah. That makes sense.
I'm a total sucker
for back covers!
[KEITA gasping]
You get it, huh!
It's like they're giving us
this magical rectangle
they've smushed
all of the game's
best selling points into,
worded and arranged
for maximum hype!
Even if the game
ends up sucking,
it's still an awesome way--!
[KEITA]
Look at her...
Totally creeped out.
[KAREN laughs]
What'd I say...?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to interrupt.
You were going on about it
with such enthusiasm.
Uh...
Don't take this the wrong way.
[KEITA]
Hm?
From where I'm standing,
you're basically perfect.
Huh?
[KAREN]
Hey, I was thinking.
If you're cool with it...
...maybe you and me could...
[screaming]
...hang out in the
school's game club?
Huh?
[TASUKU]
I win!
Yes!
Read 'em and weep!
Yeah, whatever!
I'll getcha next time!
[AGURI]
Um, Tasuku?
Cutest kitty ever!
[laughs]
Sure.
If you're into derp-ass cats.
[AGURI] Mm-hm! When it comes
to gaming, you're the bestest!
That is not a word.
[AGURI]
That cat is my best friend.
I mean, if you're gonna
keep freakin' out about it.
Cough it up. Cash?
[AGURI]
Tasuku, why?
[TASUKU]
Really?
Good luck, Tasuku!
You can do it!
Hurray! Hurray!
♪♪♪
Move it left!
Right! More to the right!
It's the stripy one!
Just quiet down.
I'm not some crane-game virgin.
What the...?!
You didn't grab the
kitty at all, Tasuku!
You suck at this!
[gasping]
[AGURI]
Ta-da! [laughs]
Lookit how fluffy it is, Tasuku!
Lookit! It's mine.
Toldja you were the bestest!
[TASUKU] Look, try not
to burst a blood vessel.
[sighs]
[TASUKU]
Diagnosis? Straight-up badass.
Check her out!
My girlfriend has as much going
on upstairs as that stuffed cat,
but when you're that
cute, whatever!
[AGURI]
Uh?
[TASUKU]
Oh, man.
I am so living my best life.
Right?
[AGURI humming]
You've been humming
since we left the arcade.
Of course I have!
Look at this adorable
cat you got for me!
I'mma cherish forever!
Heh.
[TASUKU]
Huh. That guy's in my class.
Amano, or something.
He's always glued to a handheld.
[TASUKU] Why the hell's he just
standing there all randomly?
Whatcha thinkin' 'bout, Cutie?
Oh, nothin' much.
[TASUKU] Go cry into
your cartridges, loser.
You'll never land a girl
as hot as this one.
Game over.
[KAREN]
There wasn't one,
so I filled out all the
paperwork and started one up.
But I haven't really gone
on a big recruiting push yet.
[KEITA]
Well, you are a busy person.
You, too?
[KEITA]
Uh...?
It's kind of a thing.
People bending over
backwards to indulge me
whenever I talk to 'em.
So, uh, that happens a lot?
Yup. Even my teachers
are super understanding
when I forget my homework.
[KEITA laughs]
Heck, King Koopa rolled
out all the stops for me,
and I was only there
to jump on his head!
Whoa! Uh!
Hold on a sec!
I know a lie when I hear it!
I wish! It was awkward.
That might've been
a bug, you know.
Yeah, ya think?!
How did you get King Koopa
to make small talk
and serve you tea?!
I had pulled three
all-nighters in a row
trying to turn in a
world-record speed-run.
The Koopa thing was a dream!
I should have guessed
as much from the start!
You're the one who glitched out,
Tendo, not him!
[laughs]
I'm sorry.
Kinda went off on a tangent.
That's fine.
I'm just surprised that you
liking gaming so much.
You're really into it.
[KAREN] My friends don't
know this side of me,
for the most part.
Believe it or not, the whole
reason I came to Otobuki
is 'cause it had this
god-tier game club.
[KEITA]
Huh?
It fell apart
before we enrolled,
so they took it off the list.
Oh. I never would've guessed.
[KAREN]
Yeah.
That's why...
...I gave it my all behind
the scenes last year to
breathe life back into the game
club which is why this year,
it became an official
student group again!
Uh! Congrats on
pulling that off.
Oh, stop it.
So, then what exactly
does a game club do, anyway?
[laughs] You know,
you can probably guess.
We play as a group.
But we can get serious,
too, believe me.
When it's time to
bring our A-game,
we bring it and then some.
[KEITA]
Oh. That's cool.
[KAREN]
It is!
That's why I've been looking
to enlist some new blood.
That rare student who is
a gamer through and through.
Maybe someone like...
Keita Amano.
[KAREN]
Whaddya say?
You don't mind stopping
by our club room sometime
just to give it a look, right?
What's up, Amano?
[phone vibrates]
[KAREN]
Oh, no! It's my mom!
I gotta go! She flips out
when I'm home too late.
Anyway, give it some thought!
G'night, then!
Wait for me in class
after school lets out.
I'll come get ya!
Uh... Okay.
Have a good night.
[laughs] Game club.
Ahh! Who'd have thought
fate would drop something
as amazing as this in my lap?
This isn't a dream, right?
No, of course not!
It's better than a dream!
Uh?!
Uh... Oh, good. It's just Mono.
False alarm.
[bell ringing]
[KEITA] I just need
to calm down already.
--Boo!
--[KEITA yelps]
Sorry, it took me a little
while to get here.
Oh, no, it's fine!
I was just killing
some time with this!
Huh. So you play mobile
games, too, Amano?
[KEITA]
So... very close!
Uh...
[KEITA]
Oh my god!
It doesn't matter what
I'm playing on my phone!
Let's just go check out
the club room already, okay?
Huh? Ah!
Good idea. Then, follow me!
[sighs]
[KEITA]
Forgive me, Mono.
The dating-sim gods have chosen
me, and I must heed the call!
Why, hello there.
I'm Eiichi Misumi.
[KEITA]
Uh, Tendo? What's going on?
Oh, yeah.
Guess I didn't tell you.
You're not the first person I've
invited to join the game club.
Misumi? This is Keita
Amano from Class F.
[KEITA]
Uh! It's a pleasure to meet you!
He was glued to one of
those arcade puzzle games
first time I met him.
Huh? Please don't
tell people about that!
It's kind of embarrassing.
You're kidding, right? But you
were playing it so masterfully!
Be proud!
Nah. I'm average.
[KEITA] That face when the
chosen one finds out he wasn't.
[EIICHI]
Amano.
Um. I don't have many companions
to speak of, honestly.
So I...
Well, it would mean
the world to me
if you and I could be friends.
Thank you! That'd be awesome!
No. Thank you. Really.
[gasps]
[STUDENTS chattering, laughing]
[EIICHI]
I'm not complaining,
but I'm surprised the
school approved
of a game club to begin with.
[KAREN]
I know, right?
But we're a lot less slap-dash
than you guys might be thinking.
I do run a pretty tight ship.
[KEITA]
How so?
[KAREN laughs]
It's easier if I show you.
Seeing is believing, right?
[KAREN]
Welcome to... the game club!
[knocking]
[KEITA]
Anybody in here?
Oh! This place is
the gaming mother-lode!
[GAKUTO]
Tch.
[EIICHI, KEITA]
Uh!
Sorry about him.
He isn't very personable.
Well that's a crap
thing to tell them.
How exactly am I not very
personable, huh?
Come on!
You know how you
come across to people.
Let's do this right.
The wannabe cool guy in
the headphones sitting here,
is Gakuto Kase.
Problem?
Uh! No! It's a pleasure
to meet you, sir!
[KAREN] Next! The girl
slaughtering her way
through that fighting
game is Niina Oiso.
[KAREN] She... doesn't
engage with people much
when she's in the middle
of a bout, so, yeah...
Uh, such focus.
[KAREN] You wouldn't
know it to look at him,
but Kase's one of the top
FPS gamers in the world!
Uh. Cool.
[GAKUTO] You sayin' I don't
look like a champ?
Oh, wow! That's COS , huh!
My goodness. I've never
seen a game like this one.
Uh! Have you really never
seen an FPS, Misumi?
Well, if it isn't a puzzle game,
then I don't have a clue.
Wow. Specific.
[KEITA]
Another headshot!
All the equipment in this room
was purchased with prize money
from the game
competitions we've won!
Prize money?!
[EIICHI] I'm starting to get
what you meant when you told us
you run a pretty tight ship.
All right!
Now that I've given you
the grand tour of the club,
grab a controller!
[gasps]
Let's see what you've got.
Ha, ha!
Oh, man! That was
a lot of fun, huh.
[GAKUTO]
Next match.
[KEITA]
Huh...?
[sighs] I'm a little wiped out.
I think I'm gonna take a break.
[GAKUTO]
Breaks are for noobs.
Get ready.
Good teamwork, everyone.
I'm just gonna call it a day!
[GAKUTO]
We're waiting on you.
Choose your load-out.
[KEITA groans]
[KAREN]
It's his first time here, Kase,
you should go easy on him!
But what's the point
of coddling them?
It's just going to get them
killed down the line.
[KAREN]
You're always such a sourpuss.
Our guests are gonna run
off and never look back!
[KEITA]
That was unbelievable.
You dominated every map.
Even with the bots all
turned up like crazy hard!
The bots were all set
on novice mode.
You, though.
Was today really your
first time playing COS ?
I've never had a noob
take me out three times
in a single match before.
[KEITA, KAREN gasp]
Just beginner's luck, I guess.
I tried to imitate whatever
I saw you doing
when I would look over.
That's incredible, Misumi!
And you're sure you've never
picked this up before?
[EIICHI]
Not once.
This was my first FPS.
Turns out they're pretty fun!
I guess you're natural! Bravo!
[EIICHI]
Uh... Heh. It was nothing.
I see a spark of
potential within you.
Having the presence of mind
to copy techniques
from other players
is legit one of the best ways
to work on your FPS chops.
Oh, wow. Thanks so much.
[GAKUTO]
Back to the scrub...
--Huh?
--[GAKUTO] Yes, you!
[screams] Sir!
[GAKUTO] Why the hell were
you jumping up and down
like you had a damn death-wish?!
Oh! It's because
I was kinda curious about
what sort of scenery
might be on the
other side of that wall.
[GAKUTO sighs]
What are you, a tourist?!
You're supposed to
help your teammates!
[KEITA]
Uh...
[gasps]
Don't let it bug you!
He's just really passionate
about first-person shooters.
I'm sorry, Amano.
It's fine.
[GAKUTO]
Hmph.
Don't wanna get a blood-clot!
How 'bout we all take a break?
[laughs]
This breeze is heavenly.
[KEITA]
Look at the two of them go.
They're not stopping
for anything!
What can I tell you?
They're both gamers
right down to their core.
They'd starve to death if I
didn't remind them to eat.
[KEITA]
Uh-huh... Hm.
I meant to ask before,
but what made the two of you
take up gaming in
the first place?
Uh, like, a reason?
[KAREN] Mm-hm. Can you think
back to anything specific?
What do you mean?
For example, Kasay's dad
is a mercenary,
and he trained him in the
family business as a kid,
so of course he's crazy
good at shooters.
Meanwhile, Oiso's trying
to bring her best friend
back from the dark side,
which will probably involve
defeating her in
one-on-one combat.
[KEITA]
Who are these people?!
I guess I play 'cause...
...'cause games are fun
and I like playing 'em?
[KEITA]
That was not the right answer...
Oh! Right on!
As generic reasons go,
that one's a winner!
Uh! Your turn, Misumi.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
You want to know
why I play games?
I guess my reason isn't
that compelling, either.
[sighs]
[KEITA]
Thank goodness.
I lost my memory,
and the only link to my past
seems to be my skill
at block puzzles.
Uh... I'm sorry.
It's a conversation-killer.
[KEITA]
Misumi, you traitor!
[clears throat] So,
in a nutshell, that's us!
After this meeting, do you
guys have a pretty good idea
of what our club is all about?
--[EIICHI] Uh-huh.
--[KEITA] Uh. Yeah.
I know our charter members
can be a little intimidating,
but their hearts are
in the right place,
so don't let them spook you.
And please, don't feel like you
have to be the best gamer ever
to be welcomed into our ranks.
Everyone's got room
for improvement,
no matter where they're
at when they join us.
It's our mission to foster that.
We work hard and we play hard,
every day.
And if you're still interested
in coming aboard,
just say the word!
I am! I had so much
fun this afternoon.
I would be honored
to join the club!
Why, thank you!
What do you say, Amano?
Will you be in the
game club with me?
I'd love to have you!
[KEITA]
Tendo...
Misumi...
You're gonna need help.
But stick with us and I'll have
you up to snuff in no time, kid.
Thanks, you guys.
[KEITA]
They'd be my friends.
The first ones I've
ever made here.
Yeah, they've got their quirks,
but really, don't we all?
And then, there's Tendo's smile.
[KAREN laughs]
[KEITA] Games and friendship
in one place.
I feel like I should
pinch myself.
This is one of those chances
you wait your whole life for!
[KEITA]
Nah. I think I'm gonna pass.
It doesn't look like
this club plays
the sort of games I'm into.
[KAREN, EIICHI, GAKUTO]
Huh...?
[KEITA]
You idiot!
Why?! Why did you tell her no?!
Wasn't that literally
the best possible thing
anyone could ever
have offered you?!
[phone vibrates]
[KEITA]
Uh?
[STUDENTS murmuring]
Uh!
Wh-Why are you here?
[laughs] You still chuggin'
away at that mobile game?
Okay. Anyway.
Amano. I still want
you to join our club.
So, are you game?
I admit, I'm pretty
interested in you!
Huh?!
[STUDENTS gasping]
Uh.
Mm.
[phone chimes]
Wow! That was close.
I hate to think if
I had missed it.
Uh!
Uh... I'm still right here.
Ah! Tendo!
I'm so sorry. You were talking!
But here I am, tapping away!
Where are my manners?!
No problem!
I am sorry, though.
I know you want me to join the
game club, but I can't, Tendo.
Are... Are you worried
that you might not be able
to keep up with the rest of us?
Because that's not a problem!
Kase is really good about
getting everyone up to speed!
Uh-uh. It's not about that.
That's not what the problem is.
So, what is the problem, then?
[KEITA]
It's like I told you yesterday.
The whole reason I
play games is for fun.
Once you add competition
to the mix,
I don't have a very good time.
Listen, Tendo.
The game club is a
great bunch of people.
It's not you, it's me!
I really mean that!
But, I just wanna keep playing
games the way I always have!
I...
I feel so rejected right now.
Uh! Yeah! But thanks
for the invitation,
it's cool that you
thought of me.
Much obliged!
[KAREN]
You're nothing to me, Amano!
And you, you suck at games!
It's not like I enjoyed spending
time with you or anything!
So, there!
Keep up the good work with
the game club, Tendo,
I'm rooting for you!
I mean that!
[KAREN cries]
Sure.
Okay...
[KAREN yelps]
[STUDENTS]
Uh...
[KAREN whimpers]
[KAREN cries]
[KEITA]
I wonder what set her off?
[phone vibrates]