[jet engine]
[MALE PILOT]
Attention unidentified aircraft,
please come in.
Request you immediately
transmit call sign,
or indicate emergency status.
You're in danger of violating
territorial airspace.
Alter your course now.
Warhammer to Operations,
the plane's coming
into visual range.
Hold on.
What the hell?
[JUGEI] Yes, I've named
him junior disciple.
He's the legitimate heir
to the Shinatobe Big Dipper
Style Blood Technique.
You can only
handle the Kagutsuchi.
It wouldn't even be necessary
to split the two styles
if your skills weren't so
weak and underdeveloped.
[ZAPP]
Oh, don't give me that crap!
Circulating blood from
the attributes of both flame
and wind through our bodies
and being able to
use them at the same
is completely impossible
for a human!
Even for a human as humble
and talented as myself.
[JUGEI] The upper torso
of the Blood Breed
is aiming for
the Eternal Hollow
in hopes of returning to the
core to recover and ultimately
rejoin with its other half.
[MALE PARK PA]
...anticipated disaster zone...
[ALIGURA] ♪ Ten-ta-cles!
Ten-ta-cles! Ten-ta-cles! Go! ♪
Fly into your doom,
you stupid plane!
[ALIGURA]
Yay!
[giggling]
You're so easily amused.
You've got no ambition.
--Whose fault is that?
--Here we go.
[FEMT] We had plenty of other
schemes and plans, y'know.
But we pushed them all onto
the backburner to help
you with your second
Great Collapse.
[ALIGURA] Yeah, you're
the reason we're bored.
[FEMT] You promised us your
Great Collapse was sure to be
a legendary piece of
destruction, but the truth is
you've barely even
planned it, haven't you?
It's all just some half-assed
willy-nilly fantasy, isn't it?
[ALIGURA]
Oh, the truth hurts, don't it?
Ah, shove it, you two.
Show me someone else
who could have done it.
No one even knows what
caused the first Great Collapse.
[KLAUS] The intersection
between two worlds.
Hellsalem's Lot.
Libra, a secret society
of super humans
toiling in the shadows to
preserve the fractured balance
between worlds.
These are the records
of our covert missions.
[jet engine roaring]
Bloodhummer!
Go!
[HUMMER]
Hi there!
Be honest.
You really think I
half-assed this plan?
Airplane.
Belly-to-Belly!
[KING OF DESPAIR]
You can't be serious.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Alarming! Are you seeing this
ladies and gentlemonsters?
[KING OF DESPAIR]
It's all just a game.
And I'm not
the only one playing.
[KLAUS]
You have his name?
[LEO]
I've only got half so far.
[KLAUS]
In that case...
[screaming]
[horns honking]
[LEO whooping, screaming]
[hissing]
[heart beat]
Strategy can only
take you so far.
You make your moves
and plot out your pieces
and hope it goes as planned.
What else can you possibly do?
[growling]
[ZAPP] It looks like
he's putting himself
together in reverse.
[KLAUS]
What about the passenger, Zapp?
[ZAPP]
No idea, chief.
The Blood Breed's taken up
most of my attention.
What the hell?
What's up with that aura?
Got it, Klaus!
--[alien noises]
--[electricity crackling]
[chuckles]
Damn, I'm good.
[LEO]
Huh?
[screaming]
Can't we take the stairs?
[ALIGURA]
What else can you do?
You're asking us?
[KING OF DESPAIR] Well, since
you guys know so much.
[ALIGURA] Are we still
talkin' about a game?
Man, you sound lame.
I do whatever I want,
the world be damned,
and if I don't do something,
then that's on me.
I'm not gonna blame
every little variable.
And I'm definitely
not gonna worry
over every little
action I make.
I don't buy that.
Maybe you don't
worry about it,
but you think about it.
Everyone wonders at some
point if what they're doing
has any kind of
meaning or not.
If they're ever gonna get what's
coming to them, or not.
And there's no way you can
honestly tell me you've never
wondered how big of
an influence your existence
has on the world.
Or how little.
I call heads.
It's tails.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
I always win.
What you guys don't know,
is that all my pieces are
right where I want them.
Well that was freakin' weird.
What do you think that
light could have been?
Which light d'ya mean?
You didn't see it?
[crackling]
[heart beating]
A light just shot up the side
of the building into the sky.
Like, well, kinda like that!
--[horns honking]
--[crowd chattering]
[ALIGURA]
Wow!
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Whoa, it worked?
One point for me.
Yeah. Fine.
I had nothin' to do with it.
But at least I'm still
making some progress.
[whimpering]
Wow, what was that?
Awesome! Leo!
[LEO]
Huh? What was with that color?
You saw that, right?
Tell me you saw that!
[LEO]
And not to mention...
It didn't actually
explode, did it?
It looked like an explosion!
[LEO]
This is serious!
All right, I hope
you're not dead.
[strikes clanging on plane]
I suggest you get
out of my way.
Got it, huma?
[liquid dripping]
[laughing hysterically]
Sorry there, buddy!
[laughing continues]
I didn't know this plane
was shipping sea monkeys!
[laughs]
I mean, freakishly
tall and gangly ones!
[laughing]
Wait are you translucent, too?
And really slimy!
[laughs]
You're like Jello!
Or like that Japanese
stuff, kudzu cake!
[laughing]
You are horribly rude!
Excessively so!
Ya don't say.
Don't let your guard down
or you will lose your life.
I was about to say that!
Freakin' fish face!
[ZED]
That's a Big Dipper Style blade.
He's the other pupil?
[ZAPP]
So the basics of the blade form
are the same for
the Shinatobe style.
Gotta say, it's a nice
lookin' trident.
[growls]
Careful.
[groans]
[ZED] His lower half
is torn to shreds,
certain death for any human.
But he's been locked in
battle with master fang hunters
for ten hours straight
and he's not slowing down.
I can only hope he's suffering
some fatigue as a result.
Because that's the
only chance we have.
Big Dipper Style Blood
Technique, Shinatobe!
Piercing Dragon Spear!
Sky-Slicing Strands!
[ZED]
Master!
End this beast!
Rain hellfire upon him!
Master?
[ZAPP gasps]
So, it's gonna be
like that, huh?
Ya could've at least warned
us, you old floating dishrag!
So ya wanna help?
I don't need an invitation!
--[ZAPP] Kagutsuchi!
--[ZED] Shinatobe!
--[ZAPP] Seven Hells!
--[ZED] Heavenly Winged Bellows!
[screeching]
[KLAUS]
Herlelle Lucando Lozo.
Thietkaua gi Murmhavat.
I hereby seal you!
[hissing]
Brain Grid Blood
Battle Technique,
form nine, nine, nine!
Ewiges Gefangnis!
Despise me.
Forgive me.
Resign yourself.
I only commit
such brutality...
to protect mankind!
[JUGEI]
You've managed not to fail.
Frankly, I'm amazed
you're not a pile of corpses,
but you effectively
worked together by sensing
the other's abilities and
allowing them to perform
their necessary role.
You're all barely worth
more than the paper
you use to wipe
your asses with,
and sooner or later your sheer
dumb luck is going to run out.
But you've earned the right
to keep this one.
[gasps]
Master?
[stammering]
[ZED]
I wasn't told about this.
[LEO]
Hey, are you ok?
[STARPHASE] A one-two punch
of exhaustion and shock.
I feel for the guy.
[FEMT] All your plans and
that was just a coincidence?
I told you, yes.
There's not really any
point in lying about it.
[ALIGURA humming]
[FEMT] Except for the
fact that you are a liar.
[munching]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Think what you wanna think,
but I haven't lied to you.
Or maybe I'm just not in the
mood to tell the truth tonight.
You giant liar!
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Look at this way.
Does it really matter if I had
anything to do with that?
It happened and
that's what counts.
I'm not gonna try to tell you it
was on purpose or an accident,
but you can be damn
sure if it serves me,
I'm gonna hop on board.
That make sense, or not?
You wanna hop on
board something?
I've got a nice big ride
for you right here.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Aligula! [laughs]
[ALIGURA]
Ugh!
I honestly thought it was
impossible, you maniac!
[ALIGURA] Just don't think
they're gonna come cheap.
[KING OF DESPAIR] Hey,
they're worth every penny!
[ALIGURA]
It's your head if they break.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Yeah, yeah. Thank you so much!
They're exactly what I need.
[heavy breathing]
[WHITE]
Black!
Over here!
[BLACK]
White.
White!
Stay back! It's not safe here!
I'll let you have
my stupid body!
But please, please,
leave my sister alone!
I'm begging you, okay?
But that's the only way!
If you need hands.
If you have to take,
then take what
you need from me!
[WHITE]
William?
[sinister laughter]
Nope.
My name is [no audio].
I'm sure we can help
each other out,
eh, sister?
[whistling]
Huh?
Is that you, Black?
I'm gonna need you to get
your friend's eyeballs for me.
You do that,
and I'll give you
your brother back.
That is the deal
we made, after all.
[WHITE]
But Leo's such a nice guy.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Yep.
[WHITE]
He's got a little sister, too.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
I'm aware.
[WHITE]
It reminds me of us.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Yeah, I suppose.
[WHITE]
It's just that I...
I don't wanna lose
Leo as my friend.
Impossible.
You've held it together
pretty good until now, sis.
Don't get stupid on me.
Get your head in the game before
your brother runs out of time.
Don't act like you
don't know the stakes.
We're all playing
on borrowed time,
and the game is well underway.
You're the player here, White,
Me, I'm just the banker.
And your brother,
he's the bid.
The bets are placed,
the cards are dealt.
So there's no backing out
until the game is over.
Not for any of us.
Just say my name if
you don't believe me.
--[snoring]
--[clock ticking]
[KLAUS]
You're up early.
Hi, Klaus.
Or perhaps you were
never down to begin with.
Yeah, sorry.
Let me clean up
all this mess.
[KLAUS]
Long-hand, huh?
Are you writing
a letter to your sister?
Yeah,
but,
I keep coming up blank.
I wanna write, but that's
as far as I'm getting.
So I keep staring at the paper.
Oh, thanks.
[KLAUS]
Hey, Leonardo.
It wasn't just your eyes
we welcomed here.
Not in the least.
You know that,
now don't you?
[BEN]
Black?
You mean Will?
[WHITE]
Uh-huh.
[BEN]
How'd you think of that?
[WHITE]
Duh, daddy!
You're the one who said it!
Will is like black sake
and I'm like white sake.
[BEN]
Oh, yeah.
You know that I was just
making an analogy, right?
And I was kinda drunk.
Yeah, I know.
Anyway, I still think it's cool.
Yeah?
Mom totally agrees
with me, too.
Oh?
Actually,
you know what?
I'm starting to see
how fitting it is.
My two kids,
Black and White.
[WHITE] White and black are
like the complete opposite
on the color spectrum, right?
And that's exactly
how William and I are.
[BEN]
That's right.
But even so,
from where I'm sitting,
the two of you are more
alike than you might realize.
Hmm?
Well yeah, of course
we are, Dad.
We are twins.
That you are, Mary.
There's certainly
no denying that one.
From here on out,
I want you to keep
an eye on Will.
If it ever looks like he's
about to make a mistake,
you've gotta set him on
the right track, okay?
[WHITE]
Shouldn't he look out for me?
[BEN]
You don't need it.
[WHITE] What kind of mistakes
are you talking about?
[BEN]
Uh, I guess if you ever see him
about to hurt someone,
or maybe, an animal?
[WHITE]
What? William?
I think that's the craziest
thing you've ever said!
[BEN] Yeah. No, I know
how crazy it sounds!
[WHITE laughing]
[BLACK]
Hey, White!
Hey, what's up, Black?
You wanna know something?
You are both
one and the same.
--[WHITE] What's that?
--[BLACK laughs]
[BEN]
A little wish.
[laughs]
[BEN] That you'll
always have each other,
and that you'll always
keep each other happy.
[crying]
[WHITE]
Dad.
Mom.
[KING OF DESPAIR laughs]
[ZED]
My name's Zed O'Brien.
I'm Libra's newest
charity case.
I wasn't exactly given
the most gentle introduction.
And with only three episodes
left, I am a little anxious
about what's to come,
but I guess that's all
part of the training.
I'm getting along
well with everyone,
and they're weirdly nice to me.
Excluding Zapp.
Next time on
"Blood Blockade Battlefront,"
Run! Lunch!
Run! To the end.
If it takes this much
effort just to get lunch,
well, I guess it
shouldn't be so surprising
that the rest of
life is so hard.