[camera shutter clicks]
[LEO]
Oh. You show up.
[WHITE]
Hmm? [laughs]
[laughing]
You-- hold on...
why'd you take my picture?
--Huh?
--[laughs]
Well, I mean... you've
said that you're a ghost.
So I figured
you'd... you know.
[laughing] I did say that.
'Cause that's
exactly what I am.
You know what? You're
nowhere near as normal
as you look.
I think I like you!
Get off!
What? Ah!
What the hell is that?
Where'd my wall go?
Ah, such a lovely view!
I'm sure you'll miss it.
Mr. Landlord?
Guess who struck it big
in the zoning lottery?
This building is now
a tourist attraction
slash high end hotel.
Eviction terms are clearly
stated in your lease
so I know you don't mind.
Huh?
I need you to be a pal
and pack your things
and get out in the
next 40 seconds.
Otherwise...
[DEMON growls]
[KLAUS]
The intersection
between two worlds.
Hellsalem's Lot.
Libra, a secret society
of super humans
toiling in the shadows
to preserve the
fractured balance
between worlds.
These are the records
of our covert missions.
Hey, Mr. Gilbert.
What's all this about?
He said that he was evicted.
They're apparently
turning his building
into a five-star hotel.
I can't help but feel like
we should be giving him
a larger stipend.
He's still got his other job
and he's sending
all his money home.
I thought the same thing,
and I already offered
to give him a raise,
but he said he doesn't want
any more than the basic rate.
He's a good kid.
[door opening, footsteps]
[LEO struggling]
[STARPHASE]
What's with all the blood?
[ZAPP]
I got into it
with some strung-out junkie.
Freak came at me like a
rabid lion set on fire.
So naturally, I laid into
his carotid artery.
I wonder if he's
finally dead yet.
[STARPHASE]
Was he human?
Well, judging by the way
he came apart, yeah.
--That's one way to tell.
--[ZAPP] I can't say
that I've ever heard of any
drug that lets a person
survive decapitation, though.
--Oh, no?
--Hm?
[computer typing]
[ZAPP]
I'm guessin' some creep's
makin' a mint off this stuff.
[STARPHASE]
Word is that a gram of it
trades for tens of
thousands of zeros.
Even more if you traffic
it on the outside.
On that note...
[ZAPP yells in pain]
you might wanna look at this.
[PERSON IN VIDEO]
Get the Secret Service!
Mr. President!
[ZAPP]
That was on the outside,
wasn't it?
[CHAIN]
It was in the White House,
monkey.
Is it really necessary
to call me a monkey
every chance you get?
[STARPHASE] This is bad news,
to say the least.
Chain, you start searching
for gang connections.
--Right.
--Dig up what you can
from the dealers, Zapp.
I'm on it.
Does that work for
you, huh, Klaus?
Well played, Yamakawa.
[KLAUS]
I forfeited.
[STARPHASE]
You're really into that game.
--[SONIC squeaks]
--[ZAPP] Huh? What?
[SONIC makes noise]
Oh, crap, you guys!
He ain't breathin'!
What do we do,
Mr. Gilbert?
I have to say... that truly
was an exceptional game.
Don't you die, Leo!
They'll all blame me for it!
Wake up! C'mon, you brat!
--Breathe!
--Okay, everyone's dismissed.
--Start breathing, dammit!
--Just keep me posted.
[LEO] Despite
the intense campaign
of information
gathering we launched,
we didn't find a single
source that could explain
how the Angel Scale got outside.
[breathing heavily]
[STARPHASE] They've gotta
be moving the stuff
through some fairly
deep places, huh?
[ZAPP]
There's a good chance
they've gone
underground with it.
I know the video of that freak
attacking the president
went viral throughout
the alterworld.
[STARPHASE]
Then we're just gonna
have to dig in even deeper.
[ZAPP]
Are you serious?
If we dig in any deeper,
we'll be going
to the alterworld.
--[KLAUS] KK!
--Klausie!
Thanks for keeping
a girl waiting!
--Are you hurt?
--Huh? Are you worried about me?
That's so sweet.
I tell ya, Klausie,
you're the only one
in the universe who
bothers to fret over me.
Most people are weak and
worried about themselves.
Unlike you.
No matter how strong you are,
though, you're still a lady.
And I'll always be there to
help if you're ever in danger.
C'mon, don't be silly.
I'm escorting you to
the most dangerous place
imaginable, aren't I?
[tires screeching]
[engine revving]
[KLAUS]
Grandmaster Ulchenko!
What are you doing down here?
[ULCHENKO]
Who are you?
Please pardon my abruptness.
You see, my name
is Klaus Von Reinherz.
Jerk.
[KLAUS] And I must ask
you to leave at once.
Please believe me,
this is no place
for a normal human such as you.
[ULCHENKO]
I'm not who you think I am.
Excuse me.
--[KK] He's lying, right?
--[KLAUS] Of course he is.
[footsteps]
Ah, you've arrived.
Welcome, my friends.
I'm most pleased to see you
in such fine spirits
and good health, Klaus.
It's been far too long.
Truly, it is an honor.
[KK]
Don Arlelelle Eruca Fulgrouche.
One of the alterworld's
most powerful mob bosses.
A man of his criminal
stature wouldn't normally
grant an audience
to the likes of us.
However...
And you, my new friend...
it is a pleasure to meet you.
Likewise.
Let's not expend
any further time
on pleasantries, I know
we're all eager to begin.
[KK]
Luckily for us, he's incapable
of turning down
a game of Prosfair.
Now come, let us
sharpen our minds
and enjoy this
miraculous game together.
[computer typing]
[ULCHENKO]
It truly is a beautiful game.
The infinite complexity of it
makes it a staggering
work of art.
The game has intrigued me
as deeply as chess.
Although my study of
Prosfair cannot equal
my lifelong
devotion to chess,
it's more than adequate.
I'm prepared for this day!
One moment, please!
I must ask you... Do you intend
to play two games today?
Why, of course, Klaus.
Humanity needs Mr. Ulchenko.
His brilliant mind
is one of mankind's
greatest assets.
To potentially lose his genius
would be a loss
for our whole world.
I ask that you
please reconsider.
Excuse me... I'd rather
you not speak for me
like I'm not here.
I appreciate your
concern, but I'm aware
of the stakes at hand.
Now please refrain from
overstepping your bounds.
Pfft.
[ULCHENKO]
And by the way, what makes you
so certain I'm bound to lose?
With all humility,
I can assure you of this...
there is no other human
more qualified and experienced
with this game than myself.
[ARLELELLE laughs]
I like your confidence.
--[KLAUS] Mr. Ulchenko!
--Piss off!
[KLAUS]
Just one thing!
I highly suggest
that you forget
about even trying
to checkmate him.
Huh. Then you're advising
me against winning?
That's ridiculous.
Unbelievable! Does he
really not understand
what you were saying?
If all he wants
is to play a game,
the fool would be better
off at a cafe in Paris.
Tell me your desire.
[KK]
You look worried.
Are you?
[ULCHENKO]
I'd like for my country
to receive an arsenal
of nuclear weapons.
[ARLELELLE]
Nine hours.
Hey, he'll be fine!
It's like chess,
and he's a wizard at that,
right?
[ARLELELLE]
I place the value
of that request
at a nine-hour game.
If you can hold out
for the duration
or force a draw, let
alone get me to resign,
then you will win.
No disrespect, Klausie,
but you didn't die.
You've walked out of there
alive four times now.
[ARLELELLE]
And if you manage to win,
I promise that I will
grant your request.
[KLAUS]
You don't get it.
I never walked out of
there because I won.
One more thing...
those two up front?
I request to have them killed.
No one can know
of my visit here.
They could cause quite
a bit of trouble for me.
Hmm... Klaus is not the type
of man to speak on the outside
of any events that may
occur within these walls.
[KLAUS]
I only held out
for the duration,
and I just barely made it
out of there by the skin
of my teeth each time.
[ARLELELLE] However, I
will grant your request.
In exchange, though, we
will extend the game play
to 10 hours.
As for your wager,
if you lose the game
in any fashion, you'll forfeit
the remainder of your life
to me.
[KLAUS]
The more skilled you are,
the more complex Prosfair
grows in its intricacies.
On top of that,
the more time passes,
the difficulty
increases exponentially.
I call Tor me-tor.
Dey carlio.
[KLAUS]
My warning to Mr. Ulchenko,
advising him to forgo
pursuing checkmate,
was the only method
that's kept me alive.
What's happening?
Is it getting hotter in here?
It must be.
[KLAUS]
It's his game.
He's had centuries to master it.
And I can promise you this...
there will never be a human
who can defeat him.
[KLAUS]
Mr. Ulchenko!
[ARLELELLE]
It was a genuinely close match.
It is unfortunate
he couldn't last
the remaining two minutes.
I'm overwhelmed
with gratitude, though.
The chance meeting
of our two worlds?
It truly is an auspicious
event worth celebrating!
As agreed upon...
I will now collect the remainder
of your life as my own.
I can only hope that you
forgive my discourtesy,
but I request that you wait
until after we've
played our game,
before collecting
your remuneration.
[ARLELELLE]
Absolutely not.
Well, that's what I
would normally say.
But I will take our friendship
into consideration,
although I must admit
I find your request
a bit impetuous.
So let me see... 99 hours.
If you're willing to
entertain me that long,
I'll grant your request.
I accept.
Now, then, I can't imagine
you'd travel all this way
to play me without
another request.
Information about Angel Scale.
Its supplier and their
trafficking routes.
I figured you might
be after that.
Why do your requests
always concern
such contentious
current affairs?
Even I would be placed
in a perilous position
if the source became
public knowledge.
I'm sorry, my old friend.
That's not my goal.
Don't mention it.
It's all part of the ritual,
the necessary high stakes
that create such a
miraculous tension
during the game play.
And if you can play
me for 99 hours,
I'll grant both requests.
[KK]
He's been set up!
That decrepit bastard was
going after Klaus all along!
[ULCHENKO]
Why hasn't he come out yet?
Because, you arrogant prick,
he still hasn't lost.
If the rumors are true,
then that conniving
monster in there
has spent 1,200 years
of his life on Prosfair.
10 hours was hell.
I can't even
imagine playing him
for 99 hours straight.
Who exactly is this
friend of yours?
How can he compete against
that beast like this?
[KK]
His name is Klaus Von Reinherz.
The fierce leader of our agency
and a gentleman like no other.
You could say
that he's a brutally
headstrong man.
And he has an almost
beastly vitality.
[ARLELELLE] My Gore at
F8 advances and morphs
to Level 14, and
takes your Guichard.
My Laazi has reached Barlum 55.
As you can see, my
Cain 19 and Shamain 7
are in Ozzeau-averdidact.
Covenant. Daurasex me-tor.
El arlio in full.
Venalcantos.
[door slamming]
It's been quite some time
since I've seen this
piece brought into play.
Judging by my estimation,
at the very least,
my impending offensive drive
will continue for the duration
of the next 36 hours.
Careful now...
don't break, Klaus.
I understand.
Don't hold back. I'll give
it everything I've got.
[ARLELELLE]
There is no denying
that he's an interesting man.
He put his own life on the table
in order to protect
the other one,
without even slightest
bit of hesitation.
And the information that
he seeks on his own behalf
is of such
monolithic significance
that it could
definitively reconstruct
the fate of his entire world.
So, why? Why does he
pile on further risk
with such casual abandon?
It's wholly irrational.
These humans... I'll
never understand them.
Have you come to
regret your decision?
Not in the least.
And how is that?
All I can say is, I've
made up my mind not to.
--Hmm.
--I've thought it through,
and I'm content with it.
Hmm.
Listen, Klaus... in the
fairness of full disclosure,
I think you should know
that this Ulchenko fellow
you're risking your very
life to rescue...
well, in our previous game,
and without even the courtesy
of at least feigning
some hesitation,
he requested that I
have you eliminated.
So you must see the irony here.
Tell me. This man...
is he worth the pain
you've put yourself through?
Do you genuinely
find his existence
to be worthy of salvation?
[KLAUS]
Humans are weak.
Because of that weakness,
they can act selfishly
and let fear guide
their decisions.
But... why should I let
the way they live
affect my choices?
You see? Even if I'm struck
with a thousand setbacks,
nothing will ever convince me
to alter the way I live...
...my life!
[KK]
Klaus!
[ARLELELLE]
As per our deal,
I will give you the source
behind Angel Scale.
And as for you, Ulchenko,
you are entirely free to go.
[KK]
Start raiding the locations
I'm about to give you!
Hit the scum with
everything you've got
before they catch on!
Got it?
And if any of our men fail,
you tell them
I'll personally kill
every last one of them!
[LEO] As for wherever Klaus
got that kind of information,
the truth is, none of us know
how he pulled that one off.
Just on a whim,
I happened to ask
if it had anything
to do with that game,
but as usual, they hardly even
acknowledged I was there.
Hey, ya never know.
Anything can happen
in this world.
[LEO] Anything can
happen in this world.
[WHITE and LEO laughing]
[LEO]
For example...
even a normal dufus like me
can become friends
with a cute girl.
--What?
--Uhh? Nothing.
Do you really like those?
It's not like I shot
anything that great.
Are you serious?
These are awesome.
I've been locked in here
for three whole years now,
so this is almost as
good as getting out.
And I'm just glad
I've got someone
other than my
brother to talk to.
Sure, I got ya.
[WHITE]
Huh?
--[LEO] Huh?
--Hmm?
Nothing.
They're great pictures.
You think so? Thanks.
I'll bet you've got
pretty sharp eyesight.
Actually, better than
20/10 in both eyes.
I knew it!
[BLACK] If you wish to know
where your enemy is,
look no further than
within yourself.
I bet some people
actually believe that.
But it's not true.
The enemy always comes
at you from without.
Trust me on this,
never let your guard down.
The person you'll least
expect will find you today,
and they will
try to harm you.
Next time on
"Blood Blockade Battlefront..."
Blood Line Fever.
It's far too late
for introductions, brother.
And besides, you already
know my name, don't you?