[WHITE] I'm lucky enough to have
a family that I love very much.
Benjamin Macbeth.
Emma Macbeth.
William Macbeth.
They all have it.
[dinging]
Mary Macbeth.
[buzzer]
She does not have it.
The one and only blemish
in the Macbeth family tree?
[splatter]
Well, that would be me.
[WHITE] It goes back
for generations.
Everyone in my family has been
born with psychic powers.
As a result, they've
all become casters,
a group of people
who use their powers
to help the world.
So it's a long-standing
tradition on both sides
of our family
to become a caster.
Which means I should be
a first-class thoroughbred,
and makes me even more
of a disappointment.
[crying]
[WHITE]
Trust me on this one.
Being born an average kid into
a household of special people
with special powers
is miserable.
Nothing else to call it
but terrible luck.
[grunts]
[WHITE] I put myself on
trial on a daily basis.
[bleating]
[YOUNG WHITE]
Miss Mary Macbeth!
Guilty!
[WHITE]
However.
[BEN]
Objection, your honor!
We find the
defendant innocent.
[bleating]
[WHITE]
I've got these parents.
On what grounds, exactly?
Do we have to spell it out?
You came into this world as
our one and only little girl.
Could there possibly be any
better grounds than that?
Not that I know of. That's
more than enough reason.
[EMMA] Oh, look at
those beautiful eyes.
They look just like emeralds.
[BEN]
Our priceless little treasure.
I wish. But they
really mean it.
Trying to make me
feel good about myself
only made me
feel even worse.
[EMMA]
You're so cute!
[WHITE] It's like
their unconditional love
just pointed out how
different I really was.
[EMMA]
You're so cute!
[WHITE]
Another reminder?
[crying]
[WHITE]
My older brother.
Not fair! He took it!
He took it from me!
[rumbling]
[dog barking]
Hey, Dad! Will's crying again!
[crying]
--[BULLY 1] C'mere, Wuss!
--[BULLY 2] Yeah, wussy!
[WHITE] My twin brother, born
just a few minutes ahead of me,
possessed enough power
for the both of us.
[BULLIES laughing]
[WHITE] All of the casters
had high expectations
of him, as well.
And yet,
for reasons I don't understand,
he refused to ever
use his power.
[laughs weakly]
[YOUNG WHITE] Why don't you
ever try to fight back, Will?
There's just no reason
for you to always
get your butt kicked, right?
[YOUNG BLACK]
I dunno.
[YOUNG WHITE]
Putting up with it is like
inviting them to
beat you up again.
[YOUNG BLACK]
Uh.
I know you're right, but
I'm not any good at fighting.
[frustrated grunt]
You don't have to use
your fists, you dummy!
Hmm?
Psychic powers!
Uh.
You're sitting on a gold mine
and you won't even look down!
Ugh. Yeah, I'm sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
Huh?
I don't want you to apologize!
Just use them!
That's what I want, okay?
Oh, sorry.
[sighs]
[birds chirping]
Forget it.
Get beat up. It's your life.
[YOUNG BLACK]
Mary!
Hey, um.
Thank you.
Huh?
It's just that, I try not to,
but I always get scared.
I envy you, Mary.
I'm not strong like you are.
Don't be a smart aleck.
Eh?
[WHITE] What does
he mean he gets scared?
The truth is that having
psychic powers isn't
as great as it seems.
Using them causes fatigue.
And if you're reckless,
it can even
shorten your life.
[grunting]
[splat]
[AUDIENCE gasps]
Scanning is exhausting.
Such a pain.
[WHITE] Maybe that's what
my brother's scared of.
Taking years off of his life.
Or maybe not.
Maybe he's just a wimp.
No, your brother's not a wimp.
And don't you worry about him.
Will's stronger than
he seems, he'll be fine.
I'm not worried. He can
be a wuss if he wants.
You and your mom can
be so ruthless some ti--
Uh, I meant strong-willed, so
he may come across
that way to you.
[bleating]
[BEN] Choosing not to use
the easiest option available?
Well, that strikes me as
an incredibly brave decision.
And, it's all up to him.
There's no reason for him to
force himself to be a caster.
Why should we make him do
something he doesn't want to?
[YOUNG WHITE grunting]
If he's thought it through
and that's what he's decided,
well, then, we have
to respect that.
Not to mention.
Did you forget about
what happened?
The reason Will doesn't
want to use his powers now?
Hmm?
I guess I did.
Really?
It was a pretty big
deal at the time.
Caused quite the commotion.
Hey, Will.
C'mere, you gotta hear this.
Mary just told me
that she-- [grunts]
[YOUNG WHITE] Don't listen
to him, it's not important!
Hmm?
[YOUNG WHITE]
He can't be serious about
not being a caster.
[BOTH laughing]
[WHITE] My parents were
usually boring and normal.
[BOTH]
Bye.
[WHITE] So it made me really
proud whenever they'd go off
to save the world
from whatever danger.
But more than that,
I was downright
envious of them.
Getting to use their gifts
as weapons and risking
their lives for
the greater good.
Whether they've got
psychic powers or not,
everyone dies at some point.
Considering that, you have
to put some serious thought
into what you want to
accomplish before you croak.
Particularly if you're
nothing special.
There's gotta be something.
[camera clicks]
[YOUNG GIRLS]
Cheese!
[EMMA] Where in the world
did you find that old camera?
[YOUNG WHITE]
In the closet.
Can I keep it?
Sure, why not?
It's your father's.
Do you like it?
Mm-hmm.
Well, I should get dinner
started before it gets too late.
[camera clicks]
[BEN]
You sure have taken a lot, huh?
[YOUNG WHITE]
Mm-hmm.
[BEN] Aren't there
any pictures of you?
[YOUNG WHITE]
Mm-mm.
That's not what this is about.
[WHITE]
Honestly?
It's not like I had a passion
for photography or anything.
[footsteps approaching]
[BEN]
What is it about then?
[WHITE] It's just that if
I were to suddenly die
in the next instant.
At least the last thing I'd
seen would remain behind.
[camera clicks]
And I thought that was nice.
That there'd still be
something left of me.
[gentle snoring]
But that's really all it was.
[BULLY]
Hey, little wuss sister!
That's a pretty cool toy
you've got there.
[BULLY 2]
Yeah, we like it!
You wouldn't have a problem
with us borrowing it, right?
Yeah, hand it over!
Sure, why not.
[YOUNG BLACK]
Hold it!
[BULLIES laughing]
That camera belongs to
my sister, you jerks!
Now give it back!
Are you serious?
[BULLY 1] Calm down,
your sister's the one who
said we could use it.
Even so, I want it back!
She loves that camera!
Here.
[whooshing]
[camera rattles]
Got it!
[screams]
[heartbeat]
[YOUNG BLACK]
Mary.
Why's your head on my chest?
I'm just making sure
you're still alive.
Oh, okay.
Where's Mom?
She's on the phone.
[YOUNG WHITE] Why would you
jump into the river like that?
[YOUNG BLACK]
Those guys threw your camera
and I was trying to catch it.
I guess I blew it
though, huh?
I'm sorry.
I know how much you liked it.
[YOUNG WHITE] You know that you
could have died if those jerks
hadn't pulled you
out of there, right?
Oh, yeah?
I guess it was dangerous, huh?
I'll have to thank
them for that.
[YOUNG WHITE]
What is wrong with you?
Why are you acting like this
happened to someone else?
You're so stupid,
Will, I hate you!
You've always got that dumb
look on your face like
you don't know what's going on.
I don't care about the camera!
The pictures were just
a dumb distraction!
You must've been given your
power for a reason, right?
So use it.
Or whatever else you can.
Just do something
to protect yourself!
If you had died, Will.
If you had actually
drowned in the river.
Will,
if you had died.
[YOUNG WHITE sobbing]
I couldn't bear it!
[sobbing continues]
[BOTH crying]
Hey, what's the matter?
Why are you guys wailing?
[YOUNG BLACK]
I was just thinking.
Do you remember when I broke
that mudball you made?
It was back when we
were really little.
It was such a well-made
and perfectly round ball.
And you seemed
so proud of it.
I think you showed it to me
hoping I would tell you
that you did a good job.
But it just made me frustrated.
So I couldn't help
but make it explode.
Talk about childish.
Well, yeah. We were
just children at the time.
When I did it,
I was sure it was
gonna make you cry.
But you didn't.
You just stood there in a daze.
And then you got started making
another ball, right away.
I got so embarrassed
with myself.
It felt like you
were outgrowing me.
Leaving me behind.
And it made me scared that
I couldn't control myself.
Scared of my powers.
So right then,
I made a promise to myself.
That until I became
as strong as you are,
I would keep myself from
using my psi powers.
[crickets chirping]
Okay. That wasn't the huge
commotion, was it?
Huh?
Dad told me there was some
kind of big deal that happened.
Oh.
Well, I did start
crying afterwards.
Hmm.
[giggling]
[BOTH laughing]
[YOUNG BLACK]
Hey. Listen.
Do me a favor.
Don't act like your
pictures aren't important.
You took those photos
'cuz you enjoyed it.
And you know how
good they are, right?
[YOUNG WHITE]
Mm-hmm. But--
I know!
Just look at this!
[laughs] It's awful, huh?
You made me wanna
try taking one, too.
But I'm terrible at it!
I'm not even close to being
as good as you are, Mary.
[YOUNG WHITE crying]
[YOUNG BLACK]
Whoa! Mary! I'm sorry!
You're right, I
shouldn't have done it!
It wasn't fair of me to take
your picture while you
were sleeping like that!
I'm sorry! I didn't
mean to hurt your feelings!
Please don't cry!
[YOUNG WHITE sobs]
Mary?
Thank you.
Big brother.
[YOUNG BLACK]
Hey, right back at you.
Little sis.
[YOUNG WHITE] Still, if you
are gonna be a caster,
it's time for you to
quit slacking off
and start practicing.
They try to hide it from you,
but Mom and Dad are starting
to get nervous about
what you're gonna do, Will.
[YOUNG BLACK]
Hmm.
I'm just not sure if I'm
really cut out for it, y'know?
[YOUNG WHITE]
What are you talking about?
You're perfect for it!
[WHITE]
Dad!
Mom!
Will!
[heavy breathing]
[explosion]
[coughing]
[YOUNG WHITE] And if you
ever get anxious about
going off on your own,
I'll come with you.
[gasps]
[vomits]
[coughs]
[shallow breathing]
[panting]
[WHITE]
Black!
[BLACK]
White.
White!
Stay back!
It's not safe here!
[YOUNG WHITE]
And besides,
Mom said
something one time.
She told me it
doesn't matter if a caster
is good at fighting
or if they're strong.
That's not what
they actually need.
[YOUNG BLACK]
Oh, yeah?
[BLACK] I'll let you have
my stupid body!
But please,
please, leave my sister alone!
I'm begging you!
But that's the only way!
If you need hands.
If you have to take.
Then take what
you need from me!
[YOUNG WHITE] The one thing
that a caster really needs.
It's something that you've had
as long as I've known you, Will.
[WHITE]
I really am sorry, Leo.
[energy pulsing]
[screams]
[pulsing continues]
I have to.
I don't want to do
this to you, but.
I have to get Will back.
And the only way
that I can do that.
Is for me to do what he wants.
[LEO winces]
[metallic clicking]
[WHITE]
Please forgive me.
I can't go on
living in this world.
[KING OF DESPAIR whistling]
[WHITE]
Not like this.
Not without my brother.
[whistling continues]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
You are absolutely correct
about one thing,
my dear sister.
Sooner or later,
everyone is bound to die.
Death!
Oh, death!
How ephemeral a thing.
So brief and defined.
This terminal
predestination of man.
However, I don't see
it as a tragedy.
Death is the ultimate
privilege of the living.
To exist beyond reason.
Roving lost and listless within
the confines of infinity.
Yes, be grateful for
your fleeting nature.
It's impossible for one to live
and forget about death.
The despair that is my being.
Conversely forgotten
by death itself.
There are few things
for me to embrace.
Only sleep,
and my yearning for twilight.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Mornin'.
You finally
wakin' up, brother?
Then it's about time
we got started...
with the finale!
[energy pulsing]
[crowd noise]
[quivering breath]
[WHITE]
Sonic?
What're you doing here?
[WHITE laughs]
Leo?
You're trying to find him?
[ticking]
[splat]
[SONIC whooping]
[WHITE whimpering]
[WHITE]
Hey. Sonic.
Can you help me out?
Find Leo.
[explosions]
[panting]
I think it's safe to say
this isn't your luckiest day,
is it, old god eyes?
[laughs]
As if I haven't already put you
through enough hell as it is.
Now you go and get yourself
possessed by a ghost.
[whistling]
[KING OF DESPAIR] I do hope you
realize that she's not human.
There's a barrier
in place of her heart.
It's the only thing
keeping her alive.
Nothing more than a
desperate last-ditch attempt
by her parents to keep
the feeble little brat
from croaking on them.
Lingering affection.
You. And me.
It's what's keeping us alive.
You're not the only one
who lost whatever remaining
hope you had that day.
I went through
the same thing myself.
You do understand that
it has to be this way.
Don't you, Mary Macbeth?
If there's an efficacious
method that allows you to
achieve your objective.
Then you fully embrace it,
no matter what it is.
[gun rattles]
I bid you farewell,
my sweet Mother Mary.
I did love you.
--[rumbling]
--[wind howling]
[FEMT]
Well then.
Looks like the Second
Collapse finally begins.
Of course, leave it to him to
choose today of all days.
It's so obviously
freakin' droll that it loses
any trace of humor.
Well, now what?
I mean, look how
dark it is in there.
How're we ever supposed to
find our way home in that?
[KING OF DESPAIR] Greetings,
mirthful pumpkin-heads.
Having fun out there tonight?
Playing any good tricks?
Taking some treats?
Call me the King of Despair.
I've worked really hard to
prepare an extra special show,
just for today.
I do sincerely
hope you enjoy it,
especially since you're
all performing in it.
The name of this performance
will be, let's see here.
How about "Sympathy
for the Devil."
[LEO]
I have a younger sister.
Not too long ago,
this brave, noble,
charming sister of mine
offered herself up
in place of me
and lost her eyesight.
This world around me.
The world that I
see with her eyes.
It's stunningly
beautiful, and cruel.
And now that my eyes
are closed, it shines.
Next time on
"Blood Blockade Battlefront,"
Hello, world!
Michella,
more than ever,
I have to
tell you something.