[LEO]
Ever since that fateful day,
I've been plagued
with these dreams.
Unshakable terror.
Constant anxiety.
Days filled with remorse.
They bleed over into my sleep.
I struggle to stand still,
praying for it to pass,
and then wake up
in the same place
as the day before.
With the same lack of answers.
And I realize I'm awake, but
I'm still in the bad dream.
[WHITE]
I had the most peaceful dream.
It was about my childhood.
Days filled with gentleness.
It was more memory than dream.
And it was so vivid.
So many years have passed
between now and then.
But I'll never allow those
memories to be forgotten.
Even though I know
it's only a dream.
Because this is
my reality now.
And there's nothing I can
do to change that fact.
[LEO] The loneliness
I've wrestled with,
the courage I've found,
the joy I've experienced,
the nearly-impossible-to-
shake hatred and sadness.
If I'm to face this
reality closing in on me,
what will it cost me?
What will I be left with?
Welcome home! You've finally
reached the end of your life!
Didn't know that death
was a place, did you?
Speak up, my cute
little corpse!
Ahh?
[slapping]
Well look at that!
You are alive, aren't you?
Don't lie to me!
[LEO]
I'm dead, dammit!
What will I lose?
And what can I do about it?
[NOMONAI] This fog is
downright impenetrable,
isn't it, Mister Guabara?
[GUABARA]
Yes!
--[sirens]
--[honking]
[NOMONAI] It's impossible
to see anything,
eh, Mr. Guabara?
[GUABARA]
Yes!
[NOMONAI] Do you think
that this young man
calling himself the King
of Despair is correct?
Could we truly be in the initial
stages of the Second Collapse?
Eh, Mr. Guabara?
[GUABARA]
Yes!
[traffic passing]
[ZED] Are you just gonna stand
there adding to the fog?
[exhales]
[ZED] We're supposed
to be looking for Leo.
So let's go already.
[exhales]
[train rattling]
[STARPHASE]
Klaus!
Just heard from LHOS.
They're getting ready to
repair the destroyed barrier,
but they can't initiate until
the other casters arrive.
They made a formal
request for our assistance.
The final caster's gone missing
and they need him found.
Has it already
been three years?
Or has it only
Either way, looks like
we get to stare into
the blinding
white darkness again.
[BRODY]
Yahoo!
Ha-ha-ha!
Hey, hey, hey, can you
believe this shit, man?
It's just like three years ago!
--Pipe down.
--[BRODY laughs]
Have a little class, Deldro.
I don't get how you can be so
sure that Leo's still alright.
You saw the same
video I did, right?
[PATRICK] With that
creepy little Despair dweeb
perched over his body?
Seems like bad news for Leo once
that kid's finished with him.
No. Just trust me.
I know that he's fine.
For starters, the gravitational
changes haven't begun yet.
We knew things had taken a turn
for the worse three years ago
when the Eternal Hollow opened
up beneath the whole city.
So the last barrier's
still intact.
--It's barely holding on!
--[ANGELICA] Mm-hmm.
[ELDER]
We believe that we've pinpointed
that last damaged barrier,
and if we're correct,
it's Mary Macbeth.
The girl just might be
a living, breathing barrier.
Is something like
that even possible?
[ELDER]
Mm.
Depending on their
caster's style,
barriers can come in all forms.
And the same goes for
their source of energy.
There's no precedent to state
that weaving a barrier
from a living being
is impossible.
Though it would be taboo.
My assumption is
that Mary's parents
must've performed this
shortly before their
deaths during
the Great Collapse.
Which would mean that Mary has
spent the last three years
as a buttress supporting
our dimension.
If this hypothesis is correct,
and I'm almost certain it is,
then it's imperative
that we find this girl.
And we better hope
that she's still alive.
[groaning]
[sharp exhale]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
It's so quiet.
That's never a good sign.
[winces]
Is the fog hampering
me somehow?
I feel so exhausted.
But the ghost.
I've gotta make sure
they don't find her.
Damn it.
So sleepy.
If we assume the King of
Despair is using Leo's eyes
to locate the last barrier--
Then he can't kill him
until he's done with him!
[laughs]
Hopefully. Whatever the case,
Leonardo's the key
to this pandemonium.
We have to find him
no matter what!
--[HUMMER] Hell, yeah!
--[NEYKA] Yes, sir!
Come on! Rise and
shine, boy-o!
This is a piss-poor time
for you to be deceased.
[LEO]
Who are you?
And why do you care?
[FEMT] Considering
your current situation,
what the hell does
it matter who I am?
I mean, it's not like you
can see me, right?
I'm just a passing
tourist, or terrorist,
whatever, same thing.
Doing my best to desecrate
the sacred and wake the dead.
[LEO]
I don't understand.
Are you a friend of Black's?
[FEMT]
Who's Black?
Oh, you mean his old
trusty meat bag.
I'm not his friend.
I just know the guy
living inside his body.
Oh, boy. I look away for one
second and you fall to pieces.
Depression and death
aren't the same thing.
You'll never save
the world like that.
[LEO gasps]
[grunts]
[exhales]
Listen up, Leonardo Watch.
Before you can
save the world,
you've gotta watch us
wreck it all to hell.
[coin clinking]
[FEMT]
Heads? Or tails?
[LEO]
Huh?
[FEMT]
You know the friggin' game.
Judging by that constipated
look on your face,
you've got a ton of
questions, so I'm giving you
the chance to ask them.
If you win, I'll tell you
anything you wanna know.
And if you lose.
Uh...
I leave you down here forever?
--[LEO] Huh?
--[FEMT] You're not supposed
to look so damned relieved!
You're ruining the bet!
[grunting]
[LEO]
I just--
I kind of figured you
were gonna kill me if I lost,
so it wasn't the
wager I was expecting.
[FEMT] You're worried
about me killing you?
Snap out of it, kid,
you don't need any help
--from me in that department!
--[LEO] Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Use your damn brain. Jeez.
[LEO]
Okay.
I'm feeling some
crazy déjà vu here.
I clearly remember this.
[FEMT] Let me break
this down this for you.
Ya stay here till ya die,
or you go free
and then ya die.
Either way, you're gonna
die sooner or later.
So make your
decision, young man.
Heads or tails,
which will it be?
[scooter motor]
What's wrong with you?
Aren't you worried about Leo?
Huh? Why the hell
should I waste my time
worrying about that
squinty, scruffy nut sack?
Really? Because he's
just an ordinary person!
Other than the eyes.
He's nothing more
than a normal kid!
[tires squealing]
--[thud]
--[grunting]
[KLAUS]
Stephen.
If you look hard enough,
you can still see the light.
[LEO]
My choice?
Why'd you brake like that?
I could've died!
Do you even understand
what the hell we are?
Huh?
We're Libra, you idiot!
Nothing breaks our resolve!
Not a damned thing.
And that "ordinary, normal
kid" is part of our team.
[STARPHASE] Have we done this?
Had this conversation?
[KLAUS]
Hmm.
I'm really not sure.
[STARPHASE]
Y'know, Klaus.
When I think back to the
Collapse three years ago,
it depresses the
hell outta me.
But I've got this feeling.
I honestly don't think
that today's gonna be
anything like that
waking nightmare.
Three years almost feels
like the blink of an eye.
But we've spent just about
every second of every day
during that time in training.
Training to make sure we
won't ever let it happen again.
[coin flipping]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Why are you here?
Was this on your
trick or treating route?
[FEMT]
Not at all.
I just dropped in
to check on you.
[KING OF DESPAIR] You let the
eyeballs get away, didn't you?
Of course, he refused
to play the game.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Yeah, not with you.
[FEMT]
Nor with you.
He said if we had any
questions, he wouldn't be
the one to answer them.
And then he said that he had
more important things to do
than play games so,
y'know, he left.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Talk about normal.
[FEMT]
So normal!
[KING OF DESPAIR] You could've
done me the favor of killing
for me, you know?
[FEMT] Yeah. There's not much
fun in that, now is there?
[chuckles]
Maybe not for you.
You wouldn't find
that fun, either.
--[smack]
--[STARPHASE] Ow!
[KK] Look around you, this is
not the time for reflection.
[STARPHASE]
KK.
[KK] Ha! The two of you are
starting to act like old men.
[laughs]
That video he leaked?
I've got intel.
It was filmed beneath
Saint Alanyad Central
Hospital's cemetery.
[ZAPP] Hey! I'm sick
of your ass appearing
on top of my head!
[CHAIN] You were just giving
a lecture about resolve,
but look at you.
You can't even stand on
your own two feet.
You dumb monkey.
[ZAPP] Not when
you're on my head!
[ZED]
Calm down!
--[grunting]
--[heavy breathing]
[LEO] I wonder if I actually
was relieved back there.
I'm sorry, Klaus.
I'm trying.
But I'm having trouble
seeing any light
at the moment.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
This is where I was.
Where I saw the Collapse
three years ago.
It was a thing of beauty.
The kind of sight that
grabs hold of your
values and concepts.
All of the emotions
that make a person
and turns them upside down.
An exaltation in
the purest sense.
The promise that all of
your wishes are possible.
But that was just a dream.
Our luck had clearly run out.
Mine, and those kids.
Not to mention
their caster parents.
[FEMT]
"Fallen."
"Blue." "Devil."
"King of Despair."
You've taken on
a lot of names.
"Watchman."
You've reaped
the seeds of despair
ever since the
days of Rome,
but the Great Collapse
managed to bring you
to a screeching halt.
If you're gonna
go through with this...
[coin flipping]
at least try to enjoy it.
Bring a little nonsense
to the table.
[clatter]
[yelps]
[LEO]
Whoa.
The kid's got way too much self-
righteous stubbornness to die.
I promise he's alive,
unless he's dead.
Right.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
So he thinks I'm running
short on nonsense, does he?
Ridiculous.
[energy humming]
Hell, as far as I'm concerned.
Our existence is one big joke.
Huh?
--[rumbling]
--[ZAPP, ZED] Ah!
[screaming]
What the hell?
[ABRAMS]
Are we being attacked?
[HUMMER]
How should I know!
[ABRAMS]
This feels like an attack!
[HUMMER] Whatever it is,
it's lookin' kinda dicey!
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Go on and act like it's not.
[panting]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
But this is all just a game.
Hmph.
[CROWD screaming]
[LIBRA STAFF]
What the hell's happening?
[growling]
[groaning]
Where'd they come from?
[ZED]
There's no end to them!
[STARPHASE]
What's the plan, Klaus?
[KLAUS]
Advise all Libra operatives.
In addition to
finding Leonardo.
Eradicate all
ghouls in the city!
What are those?
They're freakin' me out.
It's Halloween, Aligula!
That's the point!
I mean, zombies are
basically a prerequisite.
[explosions]
--[groaning]
--[splat]
[gunshot]
[sword slashing]
[growling]
[grunting]
[explosions]
[ALIGURA]
But they're just a distraction
to kill some time, right?
Obviously.
This is our show.
Don't we deserve
some entertainment?
[13 KINGS]
Yay!
[phone ringing]
[KLAUS]
Gilbert.
[ANGELICA]
Uh, Doctor?
It's getting really
bad up there!
William's gotta be behind this.
Not William, but the
King of whatever.
[MAN IN TRENCHCOAT]
Despair, Miss Angelica.
Right! He's destroying the city!
If it's already
getting this bad.
The real Will's
gonna be long dead
before Klaus can even get there!
Should we do something?
Maybe I should try
to help out somehow?
Like teleport up there?
[MAN IN TRENCHCOAT]
And what good is that gonna do?
I don't know! But I
can teleport, dammit!
Shouldn't I at
least try to help!
[ELDER]
Stay put.
Leave William to Klaus.
He can take care
of him just fine.
I need you here. All of
us working together.
We'll accomplish
the greater good.
[ELDER]
I'm counting on you, Klaus.
A world where a child can call
himself the King of Despair...
[whistling]
[ELDER] ...is a world
that's too sad to live in.
[KING OF DESPAIR
continues whistling]
[LEO panting]
Huh?
[wind howling]
[LEO]
What is that?
That definitely wasn't
there the last time I looked.
[laugh]
[screams]
[SONIC squealing]
[LEO]
Sonic?
Man, you scared me.
Huh?
Oh, you found my camera?
Thank you.
[SONIC chatters frantically]
[WHITE]
I'm begging you, Sonic.
Please.
You've gotta help Leo.
I'm not sure,
but I think he's in
the Central Hospital cemetery.
Is that White?
[WHITE]
Please don't.
Don't let Leo die.
Well, thanks, Sonic,
but you probably should've
taken this to Klaus.
[SONIC grunts]
[LEO sighs]
I'm guessing I've got another
trip to the ER in my future.
Good job, Sonic.
But,
can you hold onto
that a little longer?
As for me. I'm awake now,
and I'm ready to go.
[ANGELICA]
The barriers are stabilizing.
All that's left is to locate
and repair the last one.
Then we can link
them back together!
[ALL]
Yes!
[ANGELICA] Hang on!
You can do it, Doctor!
Like they said!
Just one more!
[CROWD chanting]
Just one more! Just one more!
[heavy breathing]
[ABRAMS]
There you are, Leonardo!
We finally found you!
[PATRICK laughing triumphantly]
[ABRAMS]
Huh?
[LEO screaming]
[ABRAMS]
Well, if it's not one thing.
I just can't catch
a break today.
[PATRICK]
My beautiful jeep!
[LEO]
Mr. Abrams.
We've been searching
everywhere for you.
[PATRICK] My insurance
is never gonna cover this!
[ABRAMS]
I'm glad you're alright.
[LEO]
Thanks.
I've got some unsettling
news you need to hear.
Your girlfriend, well.
She's not exactly human.
She's a barrier, isn't she?
Wait, you already knew?
That speeds things along.
She's probably the one
keeping the collapse
from going full-throttle.
But there's no telling
how long she can keep that up.
And if she were to
suddenly give out...
Yeah, I get it, you need
me to find White.
Don't worry about it.
That was already the plan.
I'll find her!
[PATRICK]
You son of a bitch!
[ABRAMS]
And those eyes of yours?
[LEO]
They're safe!
[heavy breathing]
[humming]
[LEO]
Huh?
Yoo-hoo!
[LEO]
Hummer? Where'd you come from?
[HUMMER]
I overheard.
You're trying to get to
the last barrier, right?
Where is it?
[LEO] I'm guessing it's probably
at the top of that thing.
[HUMMER]
That's a pretty good distance.
I'll give you a hand.
Ah!
[BRODY]
Full-power.
Hammer Throw!
[screaming]
Thank you, Chain!
You're alive and well.
Thank goodness.
You didn't think I--
I mean, were you
worried about me?
[CHAIN]
Oh. That's not good.
[LEO screaming]
[CHAIN] Lucky for me,
I've got the power to vanish.
Nice seeing you
one last time.
[LEO]
Why would you even say that?
[screaming]
[CHAIN] Yes. I can
confirm that Leo's alive.
[ZED]
Shinatobe!
Wind-weaving!
[LEO whimpering]
[ZED]
Leo!
You okay?
[LEO]
Thanks for the help, Zed!
Eh? Hey!
Not so fast!
[grunting]
Unbelievable.
You're seriously gonna try
to make it on your own?
Run right through this amusement
park out of a nightmare?
With no backup?
Not happening.
No way.
[LEO] Honestly. It doesn't
seem too much worse than
any other day in
Hellsalem's Lot,
but thanks, you guys.
I appreciate you
looking out for me.
[ZOMBIE DEMONS growling]
I'm glad I got to
meet all of you.
Thanks to the time
I've spent with you guys,
I can finally move forward.
[wind rushing]
[squishing sounds]
Ah!
[ZED]
Don't change the subject.
That's got nothing to do
with the matter at hand.
[CHAIN]
He's right.
[ZED] You're acting like
a reckless fool right now,
and I don't want to see
you get yourself killed.
[CHAIN]
Nor do I.
[ZED]
You do what you want,
but you need to
hear something first.
Hmm?
You've always seen
yourself as just a normal kid.
And you're right, that's
exactly what you are.
You're normally caring,
normally cheerful,
and you're normally nosy.
You've a strong moral compass,
concern for your friends,
and honor.
I know you don't see this.
But what's normal to you?
Well, it's far from it.
Everyone else would call
it courageous and noble.
It's because of
the person you are that
you don't think twice
about your own safety
when it comes to
helping your friends.
'Cause that's just
normal to you.
Alright, Leo.
Go rescue your friend.
And good luck.
[whistling]
[footsteps]
[KLAUS]
So you're the King of Despair.
One of the 13 Kings.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Oh, so you know my name?
Good for you,
Klaus Von Reinherz.
I'm almost surprised
we haven't met before.
Well, it's a pleasure.
Now get lost.
You're not the one
I'm waiting for.
[KLAUS]
That's fair.
I didn't come
to speak with you, either.
William Macbeth.
What have you done with him?
[crash]
[shattering]
Heroes like you always
rush in to save the day.
But you're never as prepared
as you thought you were.
It kind of makes me
think of that old movie.
The one about the kid
plagued with psychic powers?
Y'know, The Shining.
Spoiler alert if you
haven't seen it, but,
it doesn't exactly
go well for the hero.
[struggling]
[grunts]
[choking]
[KING OF DESPAIR] What,
you don't like games, hero?
Well, too bad.
The challenge is that you have
to protect me from myself.
Good thing you've
got a surplus of hope.
[heavy breathing]
--[rockets firing]
--[explosions]
[screams]
[flames roaring]
[hissing]
[electricity crackling]
[LIBRA STAFF] Backup requests
from zone A-3, C-1, and E-5!
[KK]
Right!
Let's go.
Onto the next location.
Come on.
The way he keeps pushing
forward no matter what
kind of reminds me of someone.
[electricity crackling]
I see it too.
[coughing]
[KING OF DESPAIR] Good lord,
you humans are so tragic.
I would call you foolish,
but you're all too innocent
and earnest for that.
I mean that's probably
why I'm still so captivated
with your species.
Even after all this time.
Just so you know.
Despite everything,
I still haven't
given up on you.
We could settle this
over a board game,
but if that's just
not enough for you,
then you leave me with no
choice but to put you down.
I see what you're doing.
You're lookin' to use me
as a punching bag
for your frustrations.
Not with the Collapse. No.
It's the eyeballs kid.
You must get pretty tired
of having to bail out
that helpless brat
all the time.
He's got some real nerve, huh?
You're wrong.
I've never considered
Leo to be a burden.
Just a friend.
That innocence you mentioned
is what illuminates the world.
And it's radiant.
As long as you
yearn for the light,
you won't be able to kill Leo.
Your despair is born out
of a hunger for hope,
and that's why
you're drawn to him.
[whooshing]
--Well, that's a surprise.
--[flames roaring]
Didn't expect a brute
like you to have such
a smooth tongue.
Don't go talking to me
like you know everything...
human.
I will now apply my Brain Grid.
Blood Battle Technique!
Go ahead and try to
save me from myself!
Hero!
[explosion]
[LEO]
Hustle!
What?
Ah! What just
happened to my eye?
This is the worst
time possible!
Whoa! Time out,
time out, time out!
--[ZOMBIE DEMONS growling]
--[LEO] I'm dead.
[ZAPP]
Every time I find you,
you're walkin' right
into a shit storm.
[gasps]
Let's try Blade One for this.
And there she goes!
Eh?
Seven Hells!
[lighter clicks on]
[flames roaring]
[ZAPP]
And that's how it's done.
[LEO]
No. It's not!
You nearly killed me,
you inconsiderate prick!
Maybe try dialing
it back next time!
[frustrated growls]
[ZAPP] You're perfectly fine,
minus a few singed hairs.
And you needed
a haircut anyway.
[LEO]
Not by fireball!
And I am not fine, by the way.
Something happened to my eye--
My eye!
Hey, you maybe wanna
make less noise?
[LEO]
What do I do?
[ZAPP] There's nothing
you really can do, right?
[LEO]
Mr. Abrams is gonna kill me.
[ZAPP]
Oh, well.
[LEO]
I've gotta keep moving.
I have to find White
before it's too late.
[ZAPP]
Sure.
[LEO] Yeah, but! How can I
find her with just one eye?
[ZAPP]
Because it's your only choice?
[LEO]
But what if my other eye--
Knock it off! It's do or die,
or die if you don't,
so no matter what it's death!
But!
Your eyes are just tools!
As long as you're not
broken, you'll manage.
[LEO]
So where there's a will
and all that crap?
[ZAPP]
Exactly.
[tires screeching]
[ZAPP] Your eyes
got you in the door.
But that's not why
you're still with Libra.
[car approaching]
[tires screeching]
[ZAPP] What the hell are
you just standing there for?
Get to it, Leo.
Don't keep the chief waiting.
[LEO]
Right!
[maniacal laughter]
Holy crap.
[KING OF DESPAIR] I really
managed to piss you off.
Didn't I?
[rumbling]
[rubble shifting]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Listen.
I know that you think
you're trying to save Will
by taking him back from me.
But it's not like I forced
him to accept me.
Not one bit.
That was entirely his choice.
He had the exact same
look on his face
that you do right now.
So just try to relax, alright?
Even if you end up croaking
beneath all that rubble.
It's okay.
I'd wager the next you
will be along to revive you.
[LEO]
No way!
I won't let that happen!
[gasps for air]
What you said.
It doesn't really sound
much better than death.
And I promise.
I'm not letting a
single person die today.
Understand?
[KING OF DESPAIR]
So what's your plan then?
Don't tell me that you're
actually thinking of using
your almighty eyes
to kill me.
[LEO]
I don't know.
Killing you is probably
the best thing to do.
But I still can't decide.
'Cause I'm not sure if
it's the right thing to do,
so I just don't know.
And that's why
I'm just gonna keep
mulling it over
for the rest of my life.
That way, next time
I see you...
well, maybe I'll have it
figured out by then.
Hopefully I'll have
a better answer for you.
[BLACK whimpering]
I don't wanna die,
I don't wanna die!
I want to live!
[gasps]
White, listen!
Please!
As long as you're trying
to take even one single
step toward the light.
No matter the struggle.
Your spirit can
never be broken!
Do you hear me?
The other half of you,
your brother,
he hasn't given up!
So how can you?
How is it okay
for you to give up?
Answer me, White!
[dripping]
[WHITE]
Will?
[footsteps]
Hey.
You okay?
[WHITE]
Something woke me.
I heard a voice.
[LEO]
Mm-hmm.
[WHITE]
Was that you I heard?
[LEO]
It could've been.
[WHITE]
Leo,
I'm so sorry--
[LEO]
It's okay.
I know.
I already found out
about your secret,
so, y'know. It's fine.
Your brother.
He wants to live.
[gasps]
[LEO] The way he is now
and the way you are.
You're the only one
who can save him.
Understand?
It's always a struggle, but
as long as you're trying
to move toward the light.
Even if it's just one step,
your spirit can
never be broken.
And that's all it takes.
Klaus told me that.
So, look, if you're afraid
because maybe the light's
just too bright,
and that's why
you're standing still.
Then I'll lead
you by the hand.
[crying]
Anytime you need me to.
Leo.
You ready?
First thing we do?
We have to save the world.
[heartbeat]
[KING OF DESPAIR gasps]
[grunting]
I'm sorry, Black!
Mutual Vision!
[grunts]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
You damn brat!
Not the eyes!
Mary Macbeth.
Ugh!
Quit fighting me!
Go back to sleep!
William.
[heartbeat]
Hey. Good morning.
White.
Same to you.
[winces]
Why's your head
on my chest?
Just making sure
you're still alive.
Oh. Right.
[WHITE]
Black.
You know...
I honestly don't care about
what happens to the world.
It's always been warped.
Even before the Great Collapse.
I know we can throw up another
barrier to gloss it over,
but I guarantee you
the same sort of thing is
gonna happen again someday.
So what's the point?
It's all the more reason to
just let it collapse now--
Enough, Black!
Don't try to lie to me.
I know you way too well,
and those are not the words
of my brave, kind brother.
[breath quivering]
I just can't bear
the idea of losing you.
I don't know what else to do.
I don't have any other way
of saving you now.
I'm sorry, but I'm scared.
Imagining a world
without you in it anymore.
That's basically the same
as the world ending to me.
[WHITE]
What are you talking about?
You know that this
planet's staying put.
The world's not gonna
end just 'cuz I'm gone.
Don't be silly.
You have to live. Okay?
You can't simply turn your
back and hide from the world.
Try not to deny
yourself a life.
This may be hard to believe,
but I promise
I'll always be with you, okay?
[cries]
[beep]
Doctor!
We've found it!
I'm picking up the last one!
Ah!
[BLACK]
The King of Despair put my body
through the wringer earlier,
so I don't have enough
strength left in me to recover
and stabilize your barrier.
So my plan is I'm gonna
try to use the strength
that's left in your body,
and I'll forge a new
barrier from it.
It's not much of a plan.
To be fully honest,
I'm not even sure it'll work.
Knowing you,
of course it'll work.
You know Mom and Dad
are with us, right?
The thing that allowed
me to be here with you
these past three years.
It was all
Mom and Dad's love.
[heartbeat]
You're right about that.
That'll never fail us.
[heartbeat fades]
[WHITE] Take care, Will.
I'll see you later.
You'll always be my hopes,
and my future.
[beep]
Ah!
[gasping]
We-- we-- we did it!
[LIBRA STAFF cheering]
[laughter]
[KLAUS] If you were going to
take any longer getting here,
I was considering
having dinner delivered.
[LEO]
Huh?
Oh, right.
Sorry about that.
[KLAUS]
It was just a joke.
[LEO]
Oh, right.
Sorry about that.
[KLAUS]
Leonardo.
[LEO]
Uh-huh?
[KLAUS]
Nicely done.
It was all you.
You saved this entire city,
and you did it
completely on your own.
Hold your head high,
Leonardo Watch.
I am so proud of you.
So proud.
Oh, right. Um...
So I-- I'm sorry about
all the trouble I caused.
I, uh--
[crying]
Sir!
[BLACK]
Are you watching this, White?
Your knight may be
a little frazzled right now
but,
he is still awfully cool.
[LEO continues crying]
[wailing]
[sniffs]
Well,
maybe not so cool.
That might be the wrong word.
But he is our hero.
[SONIC chatters]
[click]
[LEO] Hello, Michella.
How are you?
I'm finally doing well.
I'm writing this letter
to tell you that
I'm standing on
my own two feet at last.
I hope this won't upset you,
and I really hope you
won't hold it against me.
Michella.
I'm honestly doing fine.
Being in the city without you,
I still depend on your light,
but I'm managing to survive.
I probably won't get home
to see you for a while longer,
but I look forward to
telling you all about my life
in person someday.
And about the world I've seen.
[scooter motor]
I'll tell you my story.
And the story of
the people in my life.
And how they've given me hope.
[knocking]
[door creaks open]
[KLAUS] You must be
our new colleague.
Glad to have you on board.
Welcome to Libra.
[traffic noise]
[footsteps]
[whistling]
[train rattling]