[VIVIAN] One hamburger,
spaghetti with meat sauce,
and a large Peps.
Sorry about the wait.
--[crowd chatter]
--[LEO crying]
Ah, don't cry, Leo!
We're fine, now!
What's with these guys today?
Talk about awkward.
We can hear you.
[LEO]
All right, then.
[LEO, ZAPP, ZED]
Thank you God of Chow!
Huh?
[grunts]
[ZAPP] Big Dipper Style
Blood Technique Kagutsuchi!
Blade Two!
Sky-Slicing Strands,
Shining Winding Binding!
Don't make any extra
work for me, fish head!
Right. Thank you very much.
[laughs]
[groans]
They've destroyed
the diner again!
[ZAPP]
Wait. Chief?
Your timing is excellent.
Jump in and give us a hand.
All three of you.
[ZAPP squeals]
[KLAUS] The intersection
between two worlds,
Hellsalem's Lot.
Libra, a secret society
of super humans
toiling in the shadows to
preserve the fractured balance
between worlds.
These are the records
of our covert missions.
[crowd and traffic noise]
[whistling]
[all other sound fades]
[LEO]
C'mon, guys.
The boredom's killing me,
let's go get some lunch.
[ZAPP]
Oh. Already that time, huh?
Let's do it.
[LEO]
Hey, you too, Zed.
Huh? Really?
[ZAPP]
Damn it, Leo, why ya gotta go
and invite him to join us?
No matter what we
order, everything's
gonna smell like seafood now.
[LEO]
Alright, forget you.
Zed and I'll just
go without you.
If you're gonna
act like a jackass,
then you can just
eat by yourself.
Hey! Don't you ditch me!
I'll be cordial.
And I know just the place.
--[TUNA] Urgh!
--[SQUID] Ack!
--[PRAWN] Ooof!
--[CAVIAR] Mama!
What'd I tell ya? Does
that look delicious or what?
It certainly does.
Wait, you're going in there?
Wasn't that the idea?
[ZAPP]
Well yeah, but.
Isn't that cannibalism? Right?
[ZED] Do you think
fish are vegetarian?
Allow me to explain to you
how the food chain works.
Sea creatures eat
other sea creatures.
[ZAPP gags]
Your sophomoric abuse
is ignorant at best.
Every time you speak you
reveal your lack of culture.
[ZAPP stammers]
[ZED] Once that sinks in, let's
go inside and eat some seafood.
Whoa, hold on!
I just remembered that tuna was
my unlucky number for today!
[ZED] You realize that
tuna's not a number, right?
Oh, but my stomach hurts.
[ZED] Okay, forget lunch
and we'll head back.
But first, why don't you go
ahead and admit the only reason
you even joined us
was to haze the new guy.
[ZAPP mimics]
Hey, I'm all better now!
C'mon, I'll find us
another restaurant!
[ZED]
That man has many problems.
[chewing]
[vomiting]
[screaming]
C'mon in!
[ZED] Well, okay then.
That's certainly unique.
Let's try it.
Please, no! I can't eat that!
[ZED] Listen, Leo.
It's a perfectly natural thing.
A mother bird regurgitates her
food to feed to her chicks.
[vomiting]
[LEO]
Birds do! But I am not a bird!
[ZAPP] I don't have any
problems with this place.
[LEO]
Clam chowder, huh? Okay.
Sounds good to me.
[LEO screaming]
[CUSTOMERS screaming]
[FEMALE CLERK] Please, you
try be more careful, yes?
What're you talking
about, "be more careful"?
You be more careful
with what you're putting
in your clam chowder!
Mm? Cla? Machow?
This restaurant only serve
Clam [alien language], yes?
[LEO]
Next restaurant!
--[LEO screaming]
--[ROACH] Have a seat!
--[knives clinking]
--[LEO screaming]
[LEO screaming]
I suppose you're gonna eat me.
--[guns cock]
--[whimpering]
Welcome to your
new home, Master.
[squealing]
--[moaning]
--[LEO] It's dripping in there!
Dripping!
--[LEO] No way!
--[CUSTOMER] Delicious!
[screaming]
Why is every place
you guys drag me to
something out of a nightmare?
Quit putting me in
the middle of this!
[ZED]
I've done nothing but try to be
easy and agreeable, okay?
[screaming]
Deep down, I bet you're relieved
that Leo made such a stinkin'
fuss about eating at
those spots, aren't you?
You're not even trying
to hide the fact that
you're picking these
restaurants to haze me.
And besides, you were
the one about to piss
his pants in that last place.
[screams]
Our lunch hour is almost up.
Eating would be nice.
[ZAPP, ZED growling]
--[traffic noise]
--[wind blowing]
[cawing]
[STARPHASE]
The Thousand Regioka Brothers?
Yeah, that's the one.
They're an emerging mob family.
And they're lookin' to
seriously shake things up.
And when I say they're
a mob family,
I mean there are actually
a thousand brothers
from the same mother.
So?
[DANIEL] Well the other day,
a thousand used, Chinese-made,
powered suits were
exported out of the country.
Although, even after
conducting a global search,
there's no intel to be
found on the recipients.
There's strong evidence to
suggest that Juggernaut Smith,
of Varrow &amp; Hohler Freight,
smuggled them into town.
And if that theory is on the
mark, you can bet your ass
they're about to throw
one hell of a raucous party
in Hellsalem's Lot.
So, this a request
for assistance?
Exactly.
All thousand of 'em drop
on the city like locusts?
Hmph.
Well, we're screwed.
That's about one
too many to arrest.
Yeah, I don't know.
Sounds risky.
In the midst of the guaranteed
chaos, it seems like a good
chance we might
end up getting cuffed.
You've got every right
to be suspicious.
Plenty on the force that'd
love to see that happen.
But try to think big here.
An event of this magnitude?
You know word's already
gotten out to anyone
with sharp enough ears.
If the chaos gets drawn out,
there's no doubt more
dangerous elements
will take the opportunity
to make their move.
[STARPHASE]
Aw, no fair.
He knows which
buttons to push.
[KLAUS growls]
[sighs]
[DANIEL] Looks like the boss
has already made up his mind.
All right, Lieutenant Daniel
Law, it seems you're
getting your way.
Guess you'll just
have to owe us one.
You got it.
Exactly why no one's
arresting you right now.
[phone ringing]
[beep]
[STARPHASE]
Steven here.
[ABRAMS] So this is
the building you slammed
the nose of an airplane into.
[STARPHASE]
Uh, yeah.
[KLAUS] It was
strategically unavoidable.
[ABRAMS]
Of course.
It's a little unusual, huh?
Them suddenly calling
us in like this?
Yeah, to say the least.
[ABRAMS] And frankly,
I don't have a very good
feeling about it.
It's been nearly three years
since we've stood here,
before the League of
High Order Spirituals.
What brings us the pleasure
of your company today?
[clicking]
[electronic humming]
[keys tapping]
[keyboard clacking]
[crowd and traffic noise]
[whistling]
[ANGELICA]
Now, Mr. Abrams, please!
How long have we
known each other?
There's no reason to
resort to such formality.
[beam sounds]
[ANGELICA]
It just sounds silly.
Incidentally, the doctor's
running a little behind.
I'm just filling in for
him until he gets here.
[giggles]
[ANGELICA]
Hello, Klaus.
Hello, Steven.
[STARPHASE]
Long time.
[ABRAMS] I don't think I'll
ever get used to seeing it.
The world-bounding
powers you casters have.
[ANGELICA] Sure. And
just think about this.
If you stuck around, you'd be
the most normal person here.
[ELDER] Showing off
is not a sound reason
to use your power
so excessively.
How many times
must I remind you...
[ANGELICA]
Oh, hi, Doctor!
[ELDER] ...there is
a price to all things?
Our powers are
not for ourselves,
but for the people
the world over.
And they must be used
with only them in mind.
[ANGELICA]
Right.
Elder.
[ELDER]
Mm-hm.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting,
gentlemen of Libra.
And I apologize for my pupil.
Regardless, I'm glad
you could make it.
[phone ringing]
--[beep]
--[STARPHASE] 'Scuse me.
[DANIEL] It's Daniel. I got that
info on the missing units.
They're mechanized
foot soldiers
built for China's
mobile infantry.
The People's
Bright Star, type 3.
It's definitely an older
model. Almost a relic.
But they made 'em to last.
And they're sturdy as hell,
which is just one of the reasons
they were a global best-seller.
But they'd have to be, or they
never would've produced
a thousand of 'em.
So basically they're cheap,
they're nasty, and they're
the perfect instrument
for a full swarming siege.
The big question is
how do you quietly ship
that damn many of them?
[STARPHASE] Have you staked
out all the usual fixers?
First thing we did.
But we got nothin'.
[police station chatter]
--[STARPHASE] Okay.
--[beep]
We'll see what we can find.
[LEO]
Ah.
[thud]
[electricity crackling]
[ZAPP, ZED growling]
[LEO]
Please. I'm dyin' here.
I just want a normal lunch.
I'm begging you.
[whimpering]
[screaming]
[LEO]
What? Who are you?
Hear my words,
malnourished mortals!
[LEO]
The God of Chow?
Either you eat or don't eat.
Just make up your mind!
[LEO]
Yes, sir!
No matter the circumstance,
never play with your food.
[LEO] Huh? But I
don't have any food.
Remain everlastingly mindful to
eat a properly balanced meal.
[LEO]
Okay?
Make certain you never eat
two hours before going to bed.
[LEO]
What, am I on a diet?
[ZED]
Are you alright?
[LEO]
Listen, Zapp.
We have to make
up our minds.
[stomach growling]
Welcome, come on in.
We have an exquisite whitefish
for our special today.
Your entire menu
is exquisite, Artie,
and you too, Charmaine.
Well, we aim to please.
You just make
yourselves at home.
It smells alarmingly
good in here.
[posh accent] It's only on
the most rare occasion that I
can afford to drop
by this place.
I do believe I deserve to spoil
myself today though.
Yes!
[ALL]
Thank you for this food!
[glass shattering]
[WOMAN]
Artie!
[ARTIE] Oh, um, whatever seems
to be the problem, senorita?
[WOMAN]
Nuh-uh, drop the act, Artie.
Time to come clean.
[ARTIE]
Um, act?
You promised me that you'd
never come to the restaurant!
[WOMAN] Sure, and you
promised me that you
were gonna leave your wife!
When the hell is that
gonna happen, Artie?
[CHARMAINE] Hey, what's the
problem here, young lady?
[WOMAN] Oh and here
she is! The royal harpy!
Do you have any idea
how much your husband
bitches about you
when we're in bed?
It completely ruins
our sex life!
[argument fast forwards]
[ARTIE]
Ladies, please!
[CHARMAINE] You, too, you
dirty lying piece of shit!
You can both
rot in hell together!
--[screaming and stabbing]
--[ARTIE] Hey, no, stop, no!
[ALL]
Aw!
Huh. Well.
Who knew Artie was
such a ladies man?
[LEO] Yeah, Zapp, I hope you
learned a lesson from that.
You could be next.
[ZAPP]
Oh, crap, ya think so?
[LEO]
Oh, God of Chow,
things have only gotten worse.
Yo! Come on in.
Pardon the mess, but
the Grinjko Familia,
or whoever the hell they were,
kept tryin' to force me to sell
my shop so they could flip it.
Ya walked in right after I gave
the scumbags my final answer.
I just got word
their lieutenant's on
his way here to retaliate.
Figured I should give him
a taste of my passion
for this business, so I'm
whippin' up a special broth.
You guys care for a bowl?
[ALL]
Mm-mm!
[CHAIN] I'm checking out our
lead in Little Akiba right now,
but he's clean.
[groaning]
He fell asleep while playing
some porno video game.
[STARPHASE]
How can you tell?
What was it again?
It's called Starry Sleep
Station Part Six and it
just got released today!
I swore I wouldn't sleep
until I beat the 5th level,
which includes
Lemuria the Librarian,
the ruthless and dreaded
Sasha the Kazunagian,
and the Cliff Palace
Route Twins!
[heavy breathing]
[STARPHASE]
Right, so he's a nerd?
[CHAIN]
So it seems.
What the hell was that?
Hey. I'm just as
confused as you.
I've got a bad feeling
we're nowhere near
stopping this thing in time.
[LEO]
It's hopeless!
We're never gonna eat again!
We're doomed to starve!
Please, God of Chow,
he's too stupid--
[ZAPP]
What is the God of Chow?
[LEO] This is all because you
were using food for hazing.
Don't you realize you've
cursed us, you fool?
You are somehow making
a scene in this city.
It's Divine Famishment!
[LEO]
Food!
Punishment! Punishment!
This is bad.
I mean, sure, yeah,
he freaks out a lot
but this is just worrisome.
[ZED] He's starting to
speak in tongues.
So he's either receiving visions
or creating his own religion.
We need to get him some help.
Is there anywhere
he feels comfortable?
Maybe someplace that
reminds him of home?
[ZAPP]
Yeah, there is.
Y'know,
we really should've just gone
there in the first place.
What's up, guys?
Uh.
What's wrong with Leo?
[ZAPP]
It looks okay, right?
[ZED]
Yeah.
What's going on?
What's with all the tension?
[ZED, ZAPP sigh]
Okay, look.
If someone's trying to kill
you guys or something,
please go somewhere else.
[groans]
[ZAPP] All right, Leo!
Pull it together!
[ZED]
It's okay now.
You guys are acting even
more suspicious than usual.
--[chomping]
--[VIVIAN] Whatever.
What's your order?
Hamburger, spaghetti with meat
sauce, and a large Peps!
[ding]
I'll take that as well.
And I'll have the same.
[VIVIAN]
You got it.
[ALL sigh]
I'm not gonna ask what
you got yourself into,
but these guys are
a bad influence.
You don't wanna start acting
paranoid like them, do you, Leo?
What would your
parents think about you
hanging out with these two?
--[ZAPP] Hey, parents love me!
--[ZED] I am not paranoid!
[VIVIAN]
Heh, but then again,
having a group of friends
you can eat with
is always a good thing, y'know?
Mm?
[chuckles softly]
[VIVIAN] Come to think of it,
you've been bringing in
a lot of new people
with you lately.
You always just used to
sit there by yourself.
[ZAPP]
Aw, really? Is that true?
How lonesome.
Aren't you lucky you've
got me around? Huh, Leo?
Huh?
[laughs]
Yeah, actually.
I am lucky.
[VIVIAN]
Right? [laughs]
Why is your skin doing that?
You aren't blushing, are you?
Huh?
[crying]
Ah, don't cry, Leo!
We're fine, now!
[alien spaceship sounds]
[cars colliding]
[ABRAMS] I'm sorry we
had to end our meeting
so abruptly earlier, Elder.
[ELDER] Oh, it was
expected to some degree.
You are, without a doubt,
one of the busiest people
operating in this city.
So think nothing of it.
To pick up from
where we left off,
one of the barriers is damaged.
The one that was
positioned right here,
and it happened during
your men's battle
in the building above.
You mean...
Don't tell me that we...
[ELDER] Oh, no. It's not
something that can be
physically damaged, so
the blame lies elsewhere.
--You're fine.
--[ABRAMS sighs]
[ELDER] It's still more than a
little bit disconcerting though,
which is precisely
why I called you here.
[whistling]
[crowd noise]
--[panting]
--[gasps]
Hey.
[heavy breathing]
Most vexing.
Within the barrier that we
raised three years ago,
there is one among
the casters whose
whereabouts remain unknown.
Let me go! Please!
They'll kill me if
they catch me!
[struggling]
--[PUNK 1] There's the brat!
--[PUNK 2] Hey, hold her!
[ELDER] The caster couple
who was in charge died
during the collapse.
There was so much
confusion at the time,
we weren't fully
aware of the situation.
Hey! Pipsqueak!
Didn't ya hear us tellin' ya
to hold onto that kid?
[ELDER]
The thing is,
someone did manage to make
it out of there alive.
The children of the dead
caster couple, in fact.
[KING OF DESPAIR] Hey.
How about we play a game?
--[PUNK 1] Hmm?
--[PUNK 2] Huh?
What the hell are
you talkin' bout?
[KING OF DESPAIR]
If you guys win,
I'll respectfully step aside.
Hell, I'll even catch that
kid you're after for you.
Eh?
[KING OF DESPAIR] And all you
have to do is guess what I am.
[crowd noise]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Take a guess.
You already know
my name, don't you?
I only know you screwed up,
you friggin' idio--
Uh.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Guess that makes it your turn.
[whimpering]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Go on and try to figure out
what I am.
[choking, whimpering]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
But, if by some chance
your answer is wrong...
I'll have no choice but
to blow your soul to bits.
[laughs]
One of them is
even now serving
in the LHOS as a caster.
The other child though--
[WHITE]
Hey, Leo!
Mm?
[LEO]
Hey!
Why are you here?
[LEO] Well, we brought
in my supervisor.
He got sick from eating sushi.
[chuckles]
Oh, but not me though.
I don't ever eat
sea creatures.
Yeah, my other boss.
It turns out that tuna
apparently was
his unlucky number today.
Wait, what does that mean?
You do know that tuna's
not a number, right?
She speaks the truth, Leo.
The tuna is not to
be blamed here.
[ZED]
I'm sure it goes without saying,
but Zapp is his own problem.
Should've had sushi
in the first place.
[laughs]
You guys're funny.
You must be good
friends, huh?
No, we are not.
I'll stop in and check on
him before I head home.
Good idea. I kinda wanna
see him writhing too.
It was nice meeting
you, Mr. Zed.
[ZED]
Right.
[hospital ambiance]
Hey, Leo.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Sure.
[footsteps]
[WHITE]
Over here.
Mm?
Are you getting bored with
the graveyard for a change?
I've never seen you in here.
[WHITE]
Well, yeah.
Most people only come here
when they need to pray.
So it's a little unnatural
for me to be in here.
[LEO]
Hmm.
[footsteps approaching]
[clothes rustle]
[LEO]
I get that.
I guess ghosts don't really
need to pray, do they?
[WHITE]
Huh?
Heh. Exactly.
But now,
I can't help but feel
I need to say a prayer.
[whispering] For your sake, Leo.
Mm?
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Don't lie in a church.
I bet you really
do wanna pray,
but the only person
that you're thinking about
praying for is you.
After everything
you've taken part in,
you can't seriously still be
hoping for salvation.
I swear, you humans are
chock-full of hubris.
Is that Black?
[WHITE]
The All-seeing Eyes of the Gods.
I want you to give them to me.
Give me your eyes, Leo.
[monkey-like noises]