[whistling]
[MALE STATION ANNOUNCER]
The train on track number four
is bound for Shigorov Hell.
Please have your
consent forms ready.
The current survival
rate is 12 percent.
[LEO]
Whoa, that's cool.
How does someone
get an aura like that?
[BOY]
They're the kind of people
that make any room
they're in feel crowded.
The population here is
about 50 percent monster,
20 percent straight up
unknown and weird,
and humans make up the
remaining 25 percent.
But half of them have
their own strange secrets.
You know that, right?
Uh, sure.
Wait, what about the
other five percent?
[BOY] Oh, well the
remaining five percent,
they can't be seen
with normal eyes.
And whatever they are,
trust me, they're dangerous.
The intersection
between two worlds.
Hellsalem's Lot.
Libra,
a secret society of super
humans toiling in the shadows
to preserve the fractured
balance between worlds.
These are the records
of our covert missions.
[MAN 1]
Wait, Lazarollo, the mob boss,
is in the city?
[MAN 2]
Secretly, yeah.
And the HFBI director's formed
an assassination
unit to kill him.
[MAN 3]
Is Goldlake really willing
to give up retiring to Florida
just to take out Lazarollo?
[MAN 4] That tight-ass
assistant director, Tony,
must be losin' his
mind trying to stop him.
[MEN laughing]
[MAN 5] Y'know, it's nice
to get everyone together
and kick back like
this every once in a while.
You guys've been working
too damn hard lately.
[STARPHASE]
You've been going at it
full-throttle yourself, Patrick.
[PATRICK] Nah, it's
nothin' I can't handle.
I'm lucky to have
a good assistant
who keeps things
running smoothly.
And besides, arms dealin'
is my passion.
Bring on the work,
we can take it!
[STARPHASE] With the way
next week is looking,
you're gonna get
your wish there.
Yeah. I almost forgot.
[laughing]
Hey, what's the matter, Leo?
You're so quiet. You got
anything interesting to say?
Not really.
Apparently.
C'mon, big guy, speak up!
You got any dirty jokes? Huh?
[LEO]
Uh, Patrick,
I think you've had one too many!
Enough, Patrick.
How've you been, Leo?
Do you feel like you're
getting settled into the city?
[LEO]
More or less.
I mean,
I am still getting used to
some of the abrupt weirdness.
Like today on the subway.
I saw this person who
had the most incredible
crimson aura around them,
and I thought "That's awesome".
And I sort of said it out loud
because I was so surprised.
Huh?
Leonardo,
this aura,
would you say that it looked
like red wings made of light?
Stretching out from them?
[LEO]
Uh, yeah, that's right.
[STARPHASE]
All right, to be specific,
was it this color?
[LEO]
Yeah. Exactly.
[MAN 1]
Seriously?
[MAN 2]
Dammit
[LEO]
Is that a problem?
What gives?
Oh, poor naive Leo.
Let me enlighten you, my son.
Seriously? You gonna pull
the condescending mentor act?
Is that really helpful?
What you saw, my dumb pupil,
was a vampire.
[LEO]
Okay, so what did I really see?
Did I not just tell you?
[STARPHASE]
"Noble beings shrouded
with shimmering, scarlet wings".
That's how they're described
in ancient documents.
After lifetimes of research,
it's been proven that
they do actually exist,
but they remain an
elusive phenomenon,
incapable of being detected
by any optical
instruments or sensors.
[LEO]
I'm still having trouble
swallowing this one.
[ZAPP]
Then I'll beat it
down your skeptical throat,
you freakin' smart ass!
[KK]
I'm willing to bet
it was an elder
that the kid saw,
which would be
a million times worse
than the trash
we normally encounter.
[KLAUS]
With Leo's eyes,
we can actually
obtain information
that we've all only
previously dreamt of.
I think it's time
to call in the specialist.
[AUDIENCE complains]
[KK]
Is it really necessary
to call him in?
Realistically,
he'll probably show up
even if we don't ask him to.
Can you picture him
not showing up
for a situation like this?
So who is this guy?
Uh, Zapp?
Achoo!
[LEO]
"Lucky Abrams", huh?
[ZAPP]
Yeah, and to put it lightly,
he's one of the world's
most revered authorities
on vampire activity.
The chief considers
him to be his mentor.
[LEO]
His mentor?
The chief was in the
game long before this.
Then again, that
goes for all of us.
We used to be underground
monster hunters.
The chief put down plenty
of them in his solo days.
You knew all of that, right?
Sure.
[ZAPP]
Just to give you a heads up,
nobody gets a
nickname like "Lucky"
because they have good luck.
[LEO]
Then why's he called that?
[ABRAMS]
Zapp!
--There you are!
--[BOTH] Huh?
Zapp!
Jeez, look at this mess.
This city is even more dangerous
than I remember.
You'd need nine
lives to live here.
[ZAPP]
Uh, Mr. Abrams?
Not to be rude here,
but could you keep a distance
of about 10 feet from me?
[ABRAMS]
Hey!
Look at this lot!
How're you no-goodniks doing?
Klaus, my boy!
Same big old lug
you always were.
You still workin' as
hard as the world works
to keep you from doing any work?
We had a strong suspicion
that you might be
arriving shortly.
Really, I'm surprised
to hear that.
I didn't tell anyone
beforehand I was coming.
[GILBERT]
A plane unexpectedly exploded
at the airport earlier.
I doubt you need me to spell
out what exactly this portends.
[STARPHASE]
He's here.
[CHAIN]
Here he comes.
[GILBERT]
I should up my life insurance.
[ABRAMS laughs]
[ABRAMS]
You took that as
a signal of my imminent arrival?
Guess you got me there.
[ABRAMS]
I nearly got flattened
by a truck on my way over here,
but fate spared me!
[ZAPP]
Have you figured it out yet?
Where he got his nickname from
and why we're all
terrified of him?
[indistinct speaking,
animal noises]
[SHEEP baaing]
[ROOSTER crowing]
So you're Leonardo?
[LEO]
Uh, yes?
Is it true? You're the holder of
the All-seeing Eyes of the Gods?
Yes.
Why didn't you say so sooner?
[ABRAMS]
I need you
to lay your eyes on this for me.
[LEO]
Um, the hand?
[ABRAMS]
That is no ordinary hand.
You see?
This hand's our only direct
link to the Elder 13.
There is only one
known recorded incident
throughout history in
which our society.
has come face to
face with an elder.
The ghastly beast singlehandedly
took over an entire battleship,
and then, as if to mock us,
it erected a giant cross
made from the flesh
and severed limbs of
the 343 crew members on board.
Furthermore,
we've lost the lives
of 47 of our agents
who were tasked with
protecting this hand.
To be more precise,
they lost their lives
while trying to obtain
the scrap of paper
the hand is clutching.
Even separated from its body,
it tenaciously clings.
We presume there to
be a list written upon it.
A list composed of
the true names
of the Elder 13 Blood Breed.
There is power to
be found in a name
and they fervently
protect this power
beneath a cast iron
cloak of anonymity.
Now, try to read this.
With all your might,
expose their uttermost
guarded vulnerability.
Reveal their true identities!
[ZAPP]
Leo!
[KLAUS]
Are you all right?
Well that was friggin' freaky.
Huh? What the--
Um, Klaus,
the light--
It keeps
getting more--
[KLAUS]
Leonardo!
[train horn]
[ZAPP]
You see that?
That giant mystical whatever
just got taken out
by a meteorite!
I've seen some weird crap
but never anything like that!
We are not the only ones
aboard this subway, Zapp.
Please lower your voice.
I sincerely doubt something like
that is so unusual around here.
It's freakishly unusual!
[screaming]
Why the hell wasn't somebody
besides me available
to come here with you?
[ZAPP]
The chief just looks like
he's happy to take the
train for a change.
And aside from his
intelligence and luck,
he's just like any
other normal guy.
Is he gonna be okay?
His eyes are in
an amplified state.
They've become
intractably perceptive,
and his vision seems
to be peering into
the furthest depths of reality.
This just might be our chance.
[bells tolling]
We'll finally see the Elders
lurking on the other side.
[MALE TRAIN ANNOUNCER]
Yggdrashiad Central Station.
[shouting]
[crying]
[KLAUS]
Everyone okay?
[ZAPP]
I can't take any more of this!
[ABRAMS]
Alright, start recording!
It is now the 12th of September.
16 hours, 45 minutes,
and 32 seconds.
Hello all and thank
you for viewing.
If you don't know me,
I'm Blitz T. Abrams.
And on this fine day,
we stand in the heart
of Hellsalem's Lot.
We're here at Yggdrashiad
Central Station,
poised over the void itself.
Utilizing this boy's
"All-seeing Eyes of the Gods",
we are about to conduct
a search of what is
known as the
"Eternal Nothingness".
This could likely be the
first time in human history
that we're able to witness
the true forms of the Elder 13.
Listen.
Close your eyes the moment
that you feel you're in danger.
No.
Try to keep your eyes open
until the very last
second, if possible.
No.
Wait till the last nanosecond,
and once you feel
all hope is lost
and you're certain
to die a ghastly
death and all you can think is
"Stop, please, I can't
take any more!"
Wait one second
longer, then close them.
[ZAPP]
Enough, already.
[ABRAMS]
"Noble beings shrouded
with shimmering, scarlet wings."
You do remember the color
of their aura, correct?
[LEO]
Yes.
Let me know if you see one.
Or if you see all 13 of them.
Just as soon as we can confirm
that they're down there,
we'll be done here.
[ABRAMS]
Leo! Are you all right?
What the hell did you see?
[LEO]
It's really bad.
It's like a crimson
flood down there.
There's a lot more
than 13 of them.
The entire void.
It's completely full of them.
[phone ringing]
[KLAUS]
Go ahead.
[GILBERT]
Young Sir,
we have an emergency
on our hands.
We just received
a frantic request
for immediate assistance
from the HFBI.
They're engaged in combat at
the Stomcreed Avenue Station.
And there's a high probability
that they're battling an
Elder-class Blood Breed.
Yee-haw!
[GILBERT]
Their supposition is
that you are the only chance
they have at controlling them.
Please report to the
scene immediately!
[HLPD OFFICER 1]
They've broken through
the second defense perimeter!
[HLPD OFFICER 2]
They wiped them out!
[HLPD OFFICER 3]
Be careful!
They become ghouls
when they attack!
[KK]
You've done enough.
Don't bother sending any
more of your men down.
We've got it now.
[HLPD OFFICER 3]
You're going in like that?
You're not armored!
[STARPHASE]
Don't worry, we'll be fine.
Send the specialists
for special jobs.
[KK] Ugh, this couldn't
be any more tragic.
Getting paired up with
this black-hearted schemer.
[STARPHASE] Try to look
on the bright side, K.K.
This is a hell of
a lot better than
charging in after
the elders on your own.
So, hey, you're welcome.
[KK]
I've been waiting for this
for three years.
[STARPHASE]
You don't say.
Me, personally, I've
spent all my time just
wishing this day
would never come.
You're hopeless, you know that?
I've got a proclivity
for peace and quiet.
Nine, five, four.
Blood Bullet Arts!
Esmeralda. Blood Freeze style!
[KK]
Electrigger. 1.25. Gigawatt!
[STARPHASE]
Espada del Cero. Absoluto!
[MAN]
Is that them?
The friends you'd like to
see mercilessly slaughtered?
[WOMAN]
Take caution now.
There's a slim chance they
might be able to kill you.
We hold them for four minutes.
Don't tell me what to do.
[STARPHASE]
You ready?
[KK]
Always.
[ZAPP] I know you're
just doing your job,
but I need you to
do it a lot faster.
[LEO]
So that's what they--
The "Nothingness"
is swarming with those things.
How have we been
safe until now?
It would take only one of
them to infiltrate our society,
and they could blend
right in with us.
Just one of them...
could destroy our world.
--[shouting]
--[groaning]
[KLAUS]
Listen, Leonardo,
we're going to be counting on
your eyes in the days to come.
You can recognize a Blood Breed.
And their vulnerability!
[BOY]
Well, this takes me back.
Did he take that picture?
[GIRL]
Why?
[BOY]
I knew those eyes of his
were the real deal.
[WOMAN] I was really
looking forward to this,
but you two let me down.
[STARPHASE] Well, at least
we hurt your feelings.
[WOMAN]
I'd heard that you were all
some sort of anti-Blood
Breed human weapon.
But you're not
quite there, are you?
I will admit that it's
impressive how your blood
continues to attack
on a cellular level.
You would think that it would
be an effectively fatal method
since we feed on blood,
but our bodies immediately
repair themselves.
As you see, all better now.
[STARPHASE]
Do you really think
that matters, monstress?
It doesn't matter if it
takes 1,000 years or 1,500.
I promise you that
humanity will defeat you.
The day will come when
we solve the paradox
of killing the immortal.
Just wait.
I'm sure you realize I'm only
buying some time here,
but did you stop to think that
it could be time well spent?
And maybe I've stalled you
enough for the one human
with fangs that can rip
apart an Elder to arrive?
Think about that.
[KLAUS] Brain Grid
Blood Battle Technique.
Activate!
[KLAUS]
Valsh Rozzo Valctovoel Girika.
I hereby...
You know my name?
[KLAUS]
...Seal you.
Despise me. Forgive me.
Resign yourself.
I only commit such
brutality to protect mankind!
Form nine, nine, nine!
Ewiges Gefangnis!
[LEO]
None of us were even capable
of speaking afterward.
This carnage, it was the doing
of a single Elder Blood Breed.
And from what I saw,
there were close to 1,000 of
these things lurking beneath us.
Sure, we survived today,
but what happens tomorrow?
Oh, I see.
I'd got it wrong.
Maybe there is hope for us.
Maybe we can turn it around,
no matter how unlikely.
But, I do know
one thing for certain.
Getting your ass handed
to you and giving up,
they're completely
different things.
You get what I'm saying, right?
You can see them too, can't you?
Maybe I can.
Are you--
It's more fun if you
try to guess what I am.
Give it your best shot. You do
already know my name, don't you?
[LEO]
Huh?
Hello?
I'm not going back.
Yeah, but everyone's
worried about you.
[WHITE]
I don't want to go back, okay?
[phone ringing]
[BOY]
Hey, how's it going?
I see that you've been up to
your usual nonsense
lately, Femt.
Good for you.
This is your old
friend, by the way,
the King of Despair.
[squeaking noises]
[PATRICK] I'm sorry. I can't
translate that for you.
[ABRAMS] You're just gonna
have to swallow this.
The alterworld's
own specially-made,
slightly mystical
devil's tongue.
Next time on
"Blood Blockade Battlefront,"
the Tremorous Blood Hammer.
[PATRICK]
You in the next episode, Abrams?
[ABRAMS]
As a matter of fact, I am.
[PATRICK]
Well, lucky you.