[soft rock beat]
[DJ FANGO] You're listening
to WHL Mist Stream.
Coming up next is our live
listener advice program.
In this world of ours where
strange is the new normal,
we might be given a peak
or two, but naturally,
they're surrounded by valleys.
The old sentiment
"love your enemy"
comes across as quaint
at best these days.
And in this city,
the people who
preach that proverb
are typically
the first to die.
For those of you barely clinging
to the edge of this world,
hang in there.
"I just wish someone
would bother to listen to me.
If I only had
the chance to get my
problems off my chest."
If that's how you feel,
DJ Fango is here for you.
Which brings us to
our first lost-in-the-Lot
and concerned caller.
On the line with us now,
we have the pseudonymous
"The Tragedy of L."
Hello!
[LEO]
Uh!
He-Hel-Hello!
[DJ FANGO] So let's start
with a little about you,
The Tragedy of L.
Tell me what you do.
Are you a student?
[LEO]
Huh? Uh.
No, I don't!
Um, I mean, I'm not,
uh, student-ing.
I'm... uh... I-- I--
I'm an office,
I mean, worker,
I work in an office!
[hyperventilating]
[DJ FANGO]
Hey, you're doing fine.
It's okay, breathe now.
Just breathe.
[train rattles by]
[DJ FANGO] Well, how
about we jump right in?
What's troubling you today?
[LEO]
Ah, er, um,
th-th-there's so much.
To be honest, I'm not even
sure where to begin, really.
S-So much has happened,
y'know? I mean.
Since I moved to the city.
--[car collision]
--[explosion]
[DJ FANGO]
Oh, I believe it.
Anything can happen
in this world, huh?
[grunts]
[LEO] I've encountered
a lot of strange people.
And managed to get into
some super-freaky situations.
[screaming]
[LEO] But I've also met
some really incredible folks.
[DJ FANGO]
Mm-hmm.
[LEO]
And I wasn't expecting that.
[DJ FANGO] That's just some of
that "anything can happen."
[LEO] So I guess the
thing I'm worried about--
[DJ FANGO] Looks like it's time
for our first song of the day.
[LEO]
Huh?
[DJ FANGO] Here's Bump of
Chicken with "Hello, world!"
[LEO]
Bump of what?
[DJ FANGO]
And we're back.
If you're just tuning in,
we have The Tragedy
of L on the line.
We took the chance
to speak just now
during the song,
and in short,
The Tragedy of L is a rather
anxious young man
who's been beleaguered
by the routine vagaries
of our odd city
since moving here.
How long have you
been here now?
[LEO]
How, um, long?
Huh?
Le-Let's see.
Um, how, how long.
Um, well. That's a good--
[stuttering]
[DJ FANGO]
Hey, it's okay.
You're okay.
Breathe now, just breathe.
[train rattling by]
[DJ FANGO]
So I think we can agree.
This city is at the top of the
scale on the unique meter.
It's as difficult to
explain as it is to believe.
But the metaphysical metropolis
we call Hellsalem's Lot
was recently known
as New York City.
Only three years have passed
since the disastrous anomaly
labeled as the
Great Collapse occurred.
The phenomenon opened up
an interdimensional sinkhole,
if you will, a portal
colliding our world
with the alterworld beyond.
The entire island was
shrouded in a barrier of fog.
And it all happened
in a single night.
To say the least,
no one really knew--
[LEO] Yep. That's the
city I call home.
The crossroads of
weird and weirder,
Hellsalem's Lot.
And toiling in the shadows to
preserve the fractured balance
between these worlds is
the secret society of Libra.
Although it's spoken of like
it's some kind of urban legend,
it is very real.
It's just veiled in secrecy.
[KLAUS]
Welcome.
You must be our new colleague.
Glad to have you on board.
[LEO] I was taken to
their headquarters one day
due to a misunderstanding.
But the crazy thing is that
I was invited to stay on
and become a member.
[DJ FANGO] There's no doubt
these past few years have--
[LEO]
Oh. Just to be clear,
all of this is off the
record, of course.
[DJ FANGO] But, here we are
in this fog-enshrouded city.
Natives of the human world
and the alterworld
living side by side.
Of course,
It does tend to make
for a fairly precarious
living situation most days.
[DEMON roaring]
[DJ FANGO] Baffling incidents,
massive accidents,
routine violence
and everyday disasters,
it all plays out
like background music.
But, hey,
if you're looking to
alleviate boredom,
you've found the place.
[LEO] Yeah. Every day
brings a new dose of
random insanity.
It gets a little
rough some days.
But I've had my share
of happy times as well.
[DJ FANGO] You said
that you've met some
really incredible folks, right?
[LEO]
Yeah.
[KLAUS]
I'm about to use my Brain Grid
Blood Battle Technique.
So stand back.
[LEO]
Klau-- uh!
I mean--
my boss,
he's very ge-ge-ge-gentlemanly!
And, uh, y'know,
d-d-dependable and fr-friendly.
He gets too serious sometimes.
But! Not that that's bad!
[hyperventilating]
[DJ FANGO]
Hey, it's okay.
You're okay, just breathe.
Just breathe.
[train rattles by]
[DJ FANGO] I have to tell you,
you're very lucky in that area.
It's pretty rare that we
happen to hear from someone
on this program who actually
likes their work superior.
[LEO]
Oh, I don't!
I mean, not the superior
who's directly over me.
He's terrible!
I'm not sure if he's
the worst human being ever.
Zapp, give it back!
[ZAPP]
Ah.
You gotta pay for it, man!
Just give it back to me!
Or if he's the greatest
scum-sucking dirtbag ever.
[ZAPP laughs maniacally]
[grunts]
[LEO] I mean, I guess he does
have a few good aspects to him.
[ZAPP] Underestimate me at
your own peril, ya big bitch.
[gagging]
[LEO]
No, I'm wrong. He doesn't.
--He is an awful supervisor.
--[ZAPP shouting]
[DJ FANGO]
Uh-huh.
So the dark abyss you're peering
into sounds pretty deep indeed.
Is there anyone in the workplace
you can talk to about
his behavior?
[LEO]
Yeah. [laughs]
There's not much I
could really say to them.
We all agree that
he's a terrible person.
And, uh,
everyone else there is
a little strange as well.
Y'know, make that
exceptionally strange.
[DJ FANGO] It does sound
like a rather unusual place.
Listening to you explain it,
though, I get the feeling
it's a fun place to work.
But work is work, so I'm sure
there are trying times.
[LEO]
Eh?
[DJ FANGO]
So these highly eccentric,
but incredible
folks of yours,
they certainly sound
like good people to
have on your side.
Especially in this
fallen world of ours.
[LEO]
Uh-huh.
[DJ FANGO] Even this scum-
sucking superior of yours.
[LEO]
Huh?
By the way, I'm curious
as to exactly how you fit in
amongst this collection
of oddball co-workers,
Tragedy of L.
Are you just a regular guy?
[LEO]
Huh?
Oh, no. Not quite.
Yeah. Due to certain events,
and at the cost of
my sister's sight,
I now possess these
All-Seeing Eyes of the Gods.
[whimpering]
[LEO]
Ironically enough,
the powers that
sprang from this tragedy
are what led me to join Libra.
With their resources,
I might actually have a chance
at finding some clues on how
to return Michella's eyesight.
In fact, helping
my little sister
is the only reason
I came to this city.
[DJ FANGO]
Hellooo, Tragedy of L?
Are you still with us?
Uhhh, well it seems as though
he's lost, deep in thought.
Let's all take a moment to
collect ourselves during this
break from our sponsors.
[hip hop music]
This program is brought to you
by the famous Jack Funny Face
of Jack &amp; Rockets Burger Plant,
The father-daughter joint that
simply won't stay demolished,
Dianne's Diner.
Careful how you read it,
it's BobSons Clamcuhou.
As well as many
other fine establishments
throughout the city
proudly serving monsters.
[DJ FANGO]
Okay then, Tragedy of L.
I hope you're alright, now.
I mean, we are on the
air here. Help me out some.
Were you able to ruminate some
on your place in the world?
[LEO]
Y-Yeah. Sorry about that.
[DJ FANGO] Don't sweat it.
So, tell me, Tragedy of L.
What do you typically
do in your spare time?
Do you have any friends?
[LEO]
Any friends?
[DJ FANGO]
Or perhaps, a girlfriend?
[LEO]
Huh? A gir-gir-gir...
[hyperventilating]
[DJ FANGO]
Hey, you're okay. It's okay.
It's fine, just breathe.
Breathe.
[LEO's breathing slows]
[train rattling by]
Let's be friends, Leonardo!
Very best friends!
[LEO]
Uhh-Um. Um.
I mean, she's really
just a friend.
And it goes to show
that anything
can happen in this world.
But out of nowhere one day,
I just happened to meet
this really cute girl.
--[LEO laughs]
--[DJ FANGO] Oh, yeah?
That's lovely.
And you hit the nail on the
head, anything can happen.
Especially in this
mystical city in the mist.
Miracles beyond human
comprehension do happen here.
So, what's this girl like?
How would you describe her?
[LEO]
Uh.
You can just call me White!
[giggles]
I'm a ghost!
[LEO]
She, um, well...
The first time
that I met her,
she told me that
she was a ghost.
She takes stubborn to
a whole new level.
I'm not going back.
[LEO] She can get
really moody sometimes,
but never tells me why.
Oh, I'm not upset, Leonardo.
[LEO]
So, uh, well, to be honest,
I guess she's kind of
a mystery to me.
[laughs]
[DJ FANGO]
Of course, she is.
And you are not
alone, my friend.
Women remain the greatest
enigma man has ever encountered.
And that's the way
it'll always be.
They're like a question mark
followed by an ellipsis.
[laughing]
[LEO] Huh. Uh, yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
--[LEO laughs]
--[WHITE sneezes]
[DJ FANGO]
Well,
given the bittersweet
nature of our conversation.
I'd like to play
a particular song that
might hit home for you.
It's called "White Gloves."
I hope you enjoy it.
[LEO]
Yeah.
No matter how hard I look.
[LEO]
When it comes to White,
I'm completely in the dark.
[LEO] I don't even know
what was up with her that day.
Why she cried.
[WHITE] It's been about
2,000 years since mankind
was given a clean slate,
and just look how close
we've gotten to peace.
On a one-on-one basis, anyone
can understand each other.
But the human race as a whole?
Not a chance.
[snoring]
[LEO] What kind of
weight is she carrying?
What's going on
inside of her head?
[snoring continues]
[crying]
[BLACK]
Dad. Mom.
No!
[screaming]
[whistling]
--[train rattling]
--[crowd chattering]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
The population here is about
50 percent monster, 20 percent
straight-up unknown and weird,
and humans make up
the remaining 25 percent.
But half of them have
their own strange secrets.
You know that, right?
Oh, well the
remaining 5 percent?
They can't be seen
with normal eyes.
And whatever they are,
trust me, they're dangerous.
[birds chirping]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Well, this takes me back.
Did he take that picture?
[frustrated exhale]
[WHITE]
Why?
[KING OF DESPAIR]
I knew those eyes of his
were the real deal.
--[door opening]
--[BOTH laughing]
[WHITE]
Oh, hey, Leo!
See? He's the one
I told you about.
My new friend.
Uh.
[distorted noise growing louder]
[gasps]
It's you! From the subway!
Huh?
I'm afraid you've got me
mixed up with someone else.
Leo, right?
[whispering] Big brother!
[WHITE]
Remember? My big brother!
Uh.
Oh.
Yeah, hey, sorry.
White's told me
so much about you.
All good things!
Well, most of them.
[WHITE]
Huh?
[LEO]
Uh, I mean, sorry!
[laughs]
[BLACK] Sounds like you
guys are pretty good friends!
Why'd you wait so long
to introduce us, White?
It's a pleasure.
You can just call me Black.
[LEO] I told Black that
I also had a sister.
We commiserated over feeling
like worthless older brothers.
After that, we hit it off pretty
well and quickly became friends.
It's crazy, but.
Black comes from a family
of casters that played
a large role in halting
the Great Collapse.
Even crazier than that,
they've apparently possessed
Psi powers for generations.
I guess it's not that
surprising considering
what he's been through,
but he also told me that he
doesn't want to be
a caster any longer.
[BLACK] A group of people
designated as "casters" were
gathered from both worlds
and together they raised
a barrier to
suspend the Collapse.
Who knows how much worse
the conjuncture could have been
if it weren't for their
heroic actions.
And yet many mysteries
plague us still.
The precise nature of what
occurred in the center
of the void persists in evading
the best minds of both worlds.
Reliving that night?
Well, once was bad enough.
[crackling]
[LEO]
So, I'll see you later, then?
[BLACK]
Leonardo!
My sister.
She can say strange
things sometimes,
but really, she's just
an ordinary girl.
She needs a friend like you.
Hmm.
[whistling]
[LEO]
Black's a good guy.
Just look at how much
he cares about White.
The thing about
Black and White.
Now that I know them.
I don't think I could really get
by without them as my friends.
Heh.
[BLACK]
He really is a nice guy, huh?
You never told me
where you met him.
[WHITE giggles]
At the hospital.
Is there any other place?
[BLACK] C'mon, you know
what I'm asking.
Don't be coy.
I already heard the story
so be honest with me.
Okay, White?
When I met him,
he really threw
me for a loop.
That stuff about already
meeting me on the subway?
I don't know.
It's just started to weird
me out for some reason.
At the time he said it,
I just figured he must
have gotten me mixed up
with someone else.
But now,
could he have been right?
Could I have already met him?
And I just didn't
know about it?
And then, before
I realized it.
He and I--
[WHITE]
Black!
Give it a rest, okay?
Leo was just mistaken.
It happens all the time.
[paper rustles]
[BLACK]
Tell me.
What the hell are
you doing with White?
[KING OF DESPAIR] Jeez, c'mon,
you don't have to make it
sound so sordid.
She's made a friend, right?
You should be
grateful for that.
[BLACK]
You're lying!
I told you you can do
whatever you want with me.
But you promised me that
my sister would be off limits!
That was our
agreement, wasn't it?
[KING OF DESPAIR]
You're being paranoid, man,
I'm not doing anything.
[BLACK]
Tell me the truth!
[grunting]
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Get some sleep.
Let me take a turn
for a little while.
Besides, I'm really not
forcing her to do anything.
Heh.
She's doing it because
she wants to do it.
[heavy breathing]
[WHITE]
Black!
Huh?
Over here!
[BLACK]
White.
White! Stay back!
It's not safe here!
[WHITE yelps]
[BLACK] I'll let you
have my stupid body!
But please, please,
leave my sister alone!
I'm begging you, okay?
But that's the only way!
If you need hands.
If you have to take...
then take what
you need from me!
[whooshing]
[WHITE]
William.
[exhales]
[sinister laugh]
[BLACK]
Nope.
My name is [no audio].
I'm sure we can
help each other out.
Eh, sister?
[whistling]
Huh?
Is that you, Black?
[footsteps approaching]
I'm gonna need you to go get
your friend's eyeballs for me.
You do that,
and I'll give you
your brother back.
That is the deal
we made, after all.
But Leo's such a nice guy.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Yep.
[WHITE]
He's got a little sister too.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
I'm aware.
[WHITE]
It reminds me of us.
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Yeah, I suppose.
[WHITE]
It's just that I--
I don't wanna lose
Leo as my friend.
[WHITE]
Over here.
Mm?
[LEO] Are you getting bored with
the graveyard for a change?
I've never seen you in here.
[WHITE]
Well, yeah.
Most people only come
here when they need to pray.
So it's a little unnatural
for me to be in here.
[LEO]
Hmm.
--[LEO's footsteps approach]
--[clothes rustle as he sits]
I get that. I guess ghosts don't
really need to pray, do they?
[WHITE]
Huh?
Heh. Exactly.
But now, I can't help but
feel I need to say a prayer.
For your sake, Leo.
Mm?
[KING OF DESPAIR]
Don't lie in a church.
I bet you really do wanna pray,
but the only person
that you're thinking
about praying for is you.
After everything
you've taken part in,
you can't seriously still
be hoping for salvation.
I swear, you humans
are chock-full of hubris.
Is that Black?
[WHITE] The All-Seeing
Eyes of the Gods.
I want you to give them to me.
Give me your eyes, Leo.
[DJ FANGO] Well, look at that,
we're just about out of time.
So how do you feel,
Tragedy of L?
I can't honestly say that
I offered you any advice,
but did talking help at all?
[LEO] Yeah! I feel like I've got
a fresh perspective on things.
[DJ FANGO]
Glad to hear it, Tragedy of L.
With that in mind,
how about we make our way
onto the dance floor
and whirl through this
wonderful, maddening world?
I've got
the perfect song for it.
Here's Unison
Square Garden with...
[DJ FANGO and LEO]
"Sugar Song and Bitter Step."
[WHITE] For what reason was I
ever needed in the first place?
[BLACK]
What exactly do I have to do
to keep myself
from forgetting?
[WHITE] Every time I
lifted my head to look up...
[BLACK]
I was always right there.
--[WHITE] To me...
--[BLACK] To me...
--[WHITE] You were...
--[BLACK] You were...
[WHITE]
The whole world.
[BLACK]
No matter what happens,
I know that you'll be the one
thing that never changes.
[WHITE]
The one and only thing.
[BLACK]
Shaping everything.
[WHITE]
And turning it around.
Next time on
"Blood Blockade Battlefront,"
[BLACK]
Paint It Black.
This one's for you.
[WHITE]
Sure, but who am I?